[NAKAMURA]
Nano Shinonome.
I've used every single trapping
trick I have up my sleeve.
Since you still remain
out of my reach,
your system has to be
far more advanced
than I initially thought,
and I must know
what makes you tick!
For science!
Unfortunately, my various
attempts at capturing you
have garnered some unwanted
attention at school.
I must tread carefully.
[NAKAMURA]
Hm?
[CAT 24A meows]
[NAKAMURA]
Could that be...?
[gasps] Wait!
Come back!
Don't you walk away from me!
[NAKAMURA grunting]
[NAKAMURA gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
Me-Meow!
[BOY 24A]
Thanks for the food!
[MOTHER 24A] Wait for your
father to get here first!
[BOY 24A]
Aww!
[CAT 24A meows]
[NAKAMURA grunts]
[GIRL 24A] Hey, Sis,
have you seen the remote?
[GIRL 24B] I think I saw
it next to the kettle.
[CAT 24A meows]
[CAT 24A]
Meow?
[NAKAMURA]
Hm?
That's the wrong cat.
Who's out here snooping
around at this hour?
The heck are you doing?
[WOMAN 24A gasps]
Is that a thief?
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Not good!
[MAN 24A] Hey, lady!
What's the matter with you?
[NAKAMURA whimpering]
[NAKAMURA yelps]
--[thud]
--[NAKAMURA groans]
[YUUKO grunting]
--[thud]
--[YUUKO] Hm?
[YUUKO]
Huh. It's Nano.
Thank you very much
for the help.
Those books look heavy.
Not at all.
But I appreciate the assistance.
[KOUJIROU] Mm. It was
the least I could do.
Mio! Hey! Guess what I just saw!
Can you tell me later? I'm busy.
It can't wait until later!
I have to tell you
about it right now!
'Kay, go.
I just caught Nano and
Koujirou walking together
out in the hallway!
And?
[YUUKO]
Huh?
That's weird.
I thought she would totally
freak out over this.
So?
Uhh.
[gasps] Hmm.
So!
They, uh, were being all
polite to each other!
[MIO]
Hmm.
Doesn't seem like anything
out of the ordinary to me.
Huh?
[MIO]
People talk to other people.
That stuff happens all the time.
So, yeah. Is that it?
Um, guess so.
That's all I got.
All right, well, I've
gotta finish this report
before the next class.
So, you know.
I'd appreciate it if you'd
stop distracting me.
'Kay, sure. Sorry.
[YUUKO]
Well, dang. That was a buzzkill.
[MIO]
So?
Huh?
[MIO]
And then?
What happened? After?
[YUUKO gasps]
After what?
After you saw those two
being all buddy-buddy
with each other.
Well?
You were so chatty
just a second ago.
Well, um, he, uh...
Koujirou told Nano
that he thought
her big stack of books
looked really heavy.
[MIO]
And then?
And... then that's it.
[giggles]
--[YUUKO gasps]
--Oh, my gosh, Yuuko!
You are so silly, you know that?
I always knew you were
a total goofball,
but all of your crazy talk
really cracked me up this time!
[MIO chuckles]
I can't believe you made
such a big deal out of this!
You can be such a
little dummy-dumb!
It's kinda crazy how
clueless you can be!
It's fine 'cause you're dumb!
Ya idiot!
I guess I forgot to mention
that after they talked,
Koujirou and Nano
started making out.
What? No way.
You're kidding.
How could that even happen?
Well, it started off with
a little bit of smooching
here and there,
then they went to the
cafeteria for a snack,
if you know what I mean.
Turns out it was
an actual snack,
'cause they bought some bread,
but one thing led to another...
...snd suddenly, Koujirou...
[MIO]
Koujirou what?
He took his clothes
off outta nowhere!
[MIO]
He took off his clothes?
And then he mentioned
that wanted to
get his hands on
something "delicious,"
so Koujirou decided
to make his move.
[MIO]
What move?
In the courtyard.
[MIO]
The courtyard?
[BOTH scream]
I totally forgot that I gotta
do that report thing
before class, too!
Aw, crap!
We have to come up
with our own subject
for this stupid assignment?
[MIO]
But what happened?
In the courtyard...
What did they do?
Ah? You decided to get the
yakisoba bread again, I see.
[NANO]
So what? It's my favorite!
[KOUJIROU chuckles]
You sure do love that
bread, don't you?
Looks like you're the
Yakisoba Princess.
Well, uh...
What kind of bread
did you buy then?
[KOUJIROU]
Me?
I bought a sweet roll.
[NANO]
Then... does that make him...?
[KOUJIROU]
Hm? What's wrong?
It's none of your
business, so there! Hmph!
[NANO] Does that mean...
I should call him...
...the Sweet Roll Prince?
[KOUJIROU grunts]
[NANO gasps]
How delicious!
[NANO]
Then... does that make him...?
[KOUJIROU]
Hm? What's wrong?
It's none of your
business, so there! Hmph.
[NANO]
So then... does that mean...
...I should call him...
the Silky-Skinned Beauty?
[NANO]
Let's eat in the courtyard!
[KOUJIROU]
What a splendid idea.
And then I heard the
teacher ate a whale
that was caught in the wild!
[KOUJIROU]
Ha! That's preposterous!
I'm telling the truth!
But, if that's the case,
it means they went outside of
the established 200 nautical
mile exclusive fishing zone.
Oh, that's no problem at all,
because the teacher
is actually an Inuit!
[gasps]
Nano.
[NANO]
Hmm?
[KOUJIROU]
There's a crumb on your cheek.
Let me get that for you.
[NANO]
It was like a gentle moment
floating on the
soft spring breeze.
Our moment.
in the courtyard.
Our rendezvous.
Rendezvous!
[MIO] How am I supposed
to focus like this?
I can't stop thinking
about those two!
I have to know!
--[MIO] Yuuko!
--[YUUKO screams]
I was just about to
think of a topic!
Tell me what happened
between those two
in the courtyard!
[groans] Will you
stop yelling at me?
Let's see.
They were, uh...
You're useless!
[MIO] Fine then!
I'll have to find out myself!
I'll go to the
Courtyard of Eden!
[NANO]
Thank you again for your help.
It was my pleasure.
Farewell.
[MIO groans]
Huh? Mio, are you okay?
Why are you on the floor?
[MIO]
Nano.
Yes?
I heard that you were
eating yakisoba bread
with Koujirou out
in the courtyard.
And who is Koujirou? Uh--
Uh--oh, you mean that guy?
All he did was help me pick up
one of the books
I dropped earlier.
And that's it?
Yup. That's all that happened.
[MIO] But... what happened
to the yakisoba bread?
Huh? What are you talking about?
[YUUKO sighs]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
Hey!
Come on, you can trust me!
Just tell me who you like, Yumi!
Aww.
I dunno if I should.
I won't tell anybody,
but if I do, I'll give
ya a million yen! 'Kay?
All right.
But you better not tell
anyone, you promise?
Yeah, totes! [giggles]
It's Takashi.
[EMI]
Hey, everyone, listen up!
Yumi just told me that
she likes Takashi!
[NAKAMURA]
Fascinating.
[KENDO CLASS yelling]
--[MISATO] Ha!
--[YOSHINO] Head!
[MISATO sighs]
Thank you for all
your help today.
[YOSHINO giggles]
Take this.
Huh?
[MIHOSHI]
That stupid prodigy!
[MIHOSHI] It's so rare for you
stop by the dojo nowadays.
With the competition coming up,
it's good to get
some extra lessons
with our instructor
outside of school,
so I can be ready.
And having Yoshino there
also helps out with my
training a lot, too.
You're lucky, because she
usually never shows up.
What? She doesn't?
She told me she actually
starts to get worse
the harder she trains.
Like some kendo freak
of nature. [groans]
So, if you don't learn from her,
who do you normally
get your lessons from?
The instructor.
And Sasahara has also been
coming to the dojo a lot lately.
[MISATO]
Hmm.
[gasps] Sasahara?!
Since when does he
go to the dojo?
Since always?
He was going there throughout
all of middle school,
so it's really nothing new.
Yeah, but, well, I...
I guess that's true.
I don't get why you're
making such a big deal.
Aren't you in the
same kendo club?
The one at school!
No, we are not!
He's been in the drama club
ever since his first year.
[MIHOSHI]
Hmm?
Wha?!
He's part of the drama club?
Why isn't he in the kendo club?
How the heck am I
supposed to know?
If you take a weird guy like him
out of something
cool like kendo,
all you're left with
is a weird dude!
[MISATO] You don't know
Sasahara like I do,
'cause you've only ever
seen him at the dojo.
[MIHOSHI]
What do you mean?
[MISATO] I mean that his
performances in the drama club
are a bit out there,
but they're honestly pretty
unique and interesting.
[KOUJIROU] Don't be silly.
This is grape juice.
[MIHOSHI]
I guess I can imagine that.
[MISATO]
So, you get it?
What I don't get is
why you haven't just
invited him to
the kendo club yet.
It's such a waste!
What?
Why do I have to be the one
to invite him to the club?
I don't think about him.
He can do whatever he wants.
But I bet you guys could totally
make it to nationals
together with his help!
Don't hold your breath.
He ran off and joined that
stupid little drama club
of his own accord.
Who cares? I don't! That idiot!
But if you insist...
There's no need to twist my arm.
Maybe I can invite
him for your sake.
[MIHOSHI]
Oh, wow.
I can read her like a book.
--So?
--[MIHOSHI] Huh?
When does Sasahara
come to the dojo?
Uh--
Well, he stops by every
three days or so,
so I get the feeling that he'll
probably be there tomorrow.
[MISATO]
Mm...
'Kay, whatever.
It's not like I care.
[chuckles]
[MIHOSHI]
Hey, Sis.
[MISATO]
What?
You should just confess your
feelings to him already!
I don't wanna hear it from
someone younger than me!
I'm going home!
[MIHOSHI]
Sis. You're so transparent.
[BOY 24B]
It's freezing!
[BOY 24C laughs]
--Icy hand attack!
--[BOY 24C gasps]
--[GIRL 24C gasps]
--[GIRL 24D giggles]
[GIRL 24D]
See ya!
[NAKAMURA]
Fascinating.
[HAKASE chewing]
[HAKASE]
Yuck.
Mm!
[HAKASE chewing]
[HAKASE]
Ahh, so yummy!
Thank you for all of the food!
[sighs]
Hakase!
You need finish those green
onions you flicked to the side!
I think it's still
a bit too early
for me to eat green
onions right now.
What is that supposed to mean?
Regardless,
you should finish every bit
of food that's on your plate.
But the green stuff
is always bitter,
and gross, and weird,
and whatever.
[NANO groans]
If you don't finish your food,
then you don't get
snacks tomorrow.
Just look at Sakamoto
and follow his example.
He eats his food
no matter what--
[SAKAMOTO panting]
[SAKAMOTO]
Sorry. I'm just not feeling it.
Oh, no! What happened?
Aw, come here, kitty!
Are you doing all right?
[SAKAMOTO] I'm fine.
It's just a little cold.
I'll sleep it off--[sneezes]
You'll have a hard time
recovering if you don't eat.
Can you at least give it a try?
[SAKAMOTO]
I think I'll pass.
[NANO] Would it help
if I got you some milk?
[SAKAMOTO]
Don't think so.
[NANO]
Then I'm at a loss.
Do you feel like eating
anything at all?
[SAKAMOTO]
Not really.
I don't even wanna
think about it.
Oh, no.
[HAKASE] Here, Sakamoto,
you can have my green onions.
[SAKAMOTO]
Ya tryin' to kill me?!
Ooh.
[SAKAMOTO pants, sneezes]
[HAKASE gasps]
[NANO] Are you sure there's
nothing I can get for you?
[SAKAMOTO]
Yeah.
Then I'll just leave
this milk right here
in case you change your mind.
If you need anything
at all, let me know, okay?
[SAKAMOTO]
Sure.
[HAKASE gasps, coughs]
[sneezes]
I think I'm coming
down with a cough,
so can you get me
some chocolate?
Please and thank you.
Only if you eat
your green onions.
[HAKASE gasps] Why does Sakamoto
get offered stuff for free
but I don't?
[NANO] Because Sakamoto's
sick and needs the help.
Well, I'm coughing over here,
so I can be sick, too!
Sick people usually
aren't this energetic.
I just really want chocolate
and it's pumping me up!
I can be sick and excited
at the same time!
If you're actually sick,
then you have to
take some medicine.
So, do you wanna take medicine?
Forget it!
Wait, Hakase!
Did you put yourself in timeout?
[HAKASE]
Leave me alone!
You hate me, so that's
why you're being mean
and making me eat those
yucky green onions!
And you like Sakamoto more
because you're not making
him eat any onions at all!
Wait, I don't think
you understand.
Cats can't eat onions.
It's toxic for them.
[HAKASE] Well, how was I
supposed to know that?!
[sighs] You're so silly.
[HAKASE sobbing]
If I'm being honest,
I actually like you the most.
[HAKASE gasps, squeals]
Is that true?
You betcha!
[HAKASE squeals]
So can I have chocolate now
since you like me most?
[NANO]
Lemme think.
I'll let you have it
if you eat your onions.
What? No fair!
You're being the worst
most-liker of me ever right now!
Then maybe I'll just go
like Sakamoto the most.
[whines] Can you make
up your mind already?
Okay, I choose both of you!
[HAKASE groans]
[NANO giggles]
[HAKASE]
That doesn't count, Sakamoto!
[SAKAMOTO sneezes]
Which floor would you like?
The seventh floor, please,
if you wouldn't mind.
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
The thing is,
I don't remember feeling
embarrassed this year.
[IZUMI]
Now then.
Let's talk about your hopes
and dreams for the future.
[IZUMI]
Hmm.
A manga artist.
Um, that's right.
Your drawings have
always been excellent,
so this is great!
Huh? Well...
I believe in your skills.
So, feel free to
chase your dreams.
I wish you the best of luck!
[IZUMI]
Hmm?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MIO] Let's see,
Yuuko wanted the melon juice,
but what do I wanna drink?
Well, money is pretty
tight this month,
so I probably shouldn't
get anything fancy.
Just stick with the
usual banana juice.
[MIO gasps]
[MIO]
Oh! Wait! Don't roll away!
[gasps]
Sorry about that--
[MIO]
Wait. No. Yes? Yes! No!
It's him!
Koujirou's right in front of me!
[gasps]
[KOUJIROU]
I hope I didn't startle you.
You're practically a deer
in headlights right now.
[MIO gasps]
No! You're fine and
I'm fine and sorry!
[KOUJIROU]
Mm.
[MIO]
Come on!
Talk about something.
Anything at all!
So, uh...
The weather sure is
nice today, isn't it?
[MIO]
Wait! No it isn't, you idiot!
See? The sky's all
gray and gloomy!
[KOUJIROU chuckles]
[laughing]
That was rich.
[MIO]
Yeah.
By the way, miss,
might this coin belong to you?
[MIO]
Uh, yes!
Is that right?
Well, this is
certainly a surprise.
Huh? 'Kay, sure.
Perhaps I was fated to come
across you and this coin.
Huh?
This just so happens
to be the only day
I've forgotten to bring my
wallet with me to school.
And right as my throat
was becoming parched,
I was conveniently walking
near a vending machine.
And lo, I picked up this coin.
The heavens...
are shining down on me.
[KOUJIROU]
In a way,
the drink I'm to receive
is like ambrosia,
passed down to me
directly from on high.
[KOUJIROU chuckles]
[MIO]
Um...
[KOUJIROU inhales]
[sighs]
This vending machine...
Huh! Looks like it can
be quite the prankster!
Oh! Yeah!
To think.
A simple dispenser of drinks
managed to get the best me.
Must be a bold contraption
to be able to pull off
such an admirable feat.
I like it!
You deserve my coin,
you dastardly device!
Uh, Koujirou?
Shh.
[MIO]
I don't really know why, but...
...I feel like I've gotten
a little closer to him.
[YUUKO]
Mio! Where's my juice?
[MISATO sighs]
[MISATO] I wonder if she was
trying to tell me something.
Yoshino is so
strong and skilled,
she's practically unstoppable.
[MISATO]
The Knight.
What does it mean?
What do I do with it?
Confess your feelings already!
[gasps]
[door opens]
Hey, Sis, the bath is free now.
Uh--
[MIO]
I wonder.
Is Koujirou looking at
the moon right now, too?
[YOSHINO]
Sasahara!
You're not half bad, y'know!
You should come back and
train with me sometime!
[KOUJIROU]
Mm.
Cool!
I might even teach you
my secret move next time!
[MIO screams]
Sis!
--[YOSHINO chuckles]
--[MIO gasps]
Look, what's that over there?
Hm?
Sisters!
[MIO sighs]
Don't barge into my room
and scare me like that!
I wasn't interrupting
a special moment, was I?
[gasps]
[MIO]
No, of course not!
Don't worry about it!
[YOSHINO]
Are you blushing?
[MIO]
No! I'm not!
Just leave me alone!
[VENDING MACHINE]
I'm a vending machine,
and here's my MO.
When you're low on cash
and need a snack,
we'll eat your change
and won't give it back!
Respect my law!
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 25.
Look forward to it!