[school bell rings]
[FEMALE STUDENT 21A, 21B giggle]
[YUUKO groans] Lunch time,
so I'm out of the woods!
I can't believe
you got away with
not doing your homework again.
It's about time that I
had some good luck, Mio.
I was getting tired of having to
stand out in the
hallway every day.
Maybe things are
looking up for me.
Just do your homework.
[YUUKO chuckles]
Y'know what'd be great?
You getting me a juice
to celebrate my luck!
Huh?
[YUUKO gasping]
[TAKASAKI] Young lady.
We need to have a little chat
about your missing assignments,
so please come to the
faculty room immediately.
Okay.
[MIO]
Maybe I should get her a juice.
[WOMAN 21A]
Hey! I'm over here!
[MAN 21A]
Oh, hey! I'm sorry.
Were you waiting long?
[WOMAN 21A]
Not at all!
I actually just got here myself.
[FE laughing]
Sis sure is being extra loud
with her friends tonight.
[FE]
'Kay, so, I gotta know.
How are "things"?
--[WEBOSHII] Hm?
--How's what now?
Don't you be shy!
Come on!
I'm talkin' about you and
Koujirou's love life.
[screams]
Why would I even think about
marrying and spending my
life with that weirdo?
--[WEBOSHII laughing]
--What? I never mentioned that!
--[FE yelps]
--And children?
You can forget it!
[FE whines]
I hear ya loud and clear!
You, Koujirou, and his goat
already have a long and happy
life planned out together!
[MISATO gasps]
No, we don't.
So, what's been going
on with you, Weboshii?
Huh? Who, me?
Nothing you need to know about.
Aww, hey, you can tell me!
Is there somebody
you have your eye on?
[giggles] Uh-huh.
--[WEBOSHII laughing]
--Just spit it out!
--I wanna know!
Stop it, stop it! [laughs]
Okay! I'll tell you...
[FE] I'm not stopping
till you say who it is!
[laughing]
All right! As soon
as you let me go!
[FE, WEBOSHII laughing]
You better speak up
right now, or else!
Ow!
I already said I'd tell you!
Sorry. I was having so much fun,
I guess I got carried away.
So? Give us the juicy details!
I wanna know more about
this guy you like!
[WEBOSHII] Hmm. I wouldn't say
that I like him, not yet anyway.
Sure, I'm interested, but I
don't even know his name.
He's that one cool
guy with the mohawk.
--Ahh.
--It's that guy.
Oh, so you know who I'm
talking about, then?
Everybody knows about him.
He's pretty popular with
that crazy hairdo of his.
Of course we'd know him.
But why are you interested in
him of all people, Weboshii?
[WEBOSHII]
Hmm.
I guess he kinda... [chuckles]
...gives off a bad-boy vibe.
[FE, MISATO gasp]
I dunno, there's something
about the dangerous type.
He totally seems like
one of those, right?
Yeah, definitely.
And his mohawk is
like a bad-boy beacon!
Get this. I saw him
the other day,
and he was being a good,
upstanding member of society.
[MISATO, WEBOSHII laughing]
[WEBOSHII]
Yeah, okay!
[MISATO] The only thing that's
upstanding is his hair!
I'm serious. I know what I saw.
He was watering the
school's flowers.
What? Get outta here!
[FE]
Oh, yeah, and then, he, like,
even fed the plants with
this fertilizer stuff.
Oh, wow!
I never thought
he'd be so sweet!
You can't judge a book
by its cover, huh?
Yeah, you got that right.
I guess he isn't
a punk after all.
And I think I might actually
like him more now that I know.
Yeah I get what you mean.
I prefer it when
guys are nice, too.
So does that mean there's
someone you've got
the hots for right now?
[FE]
What, me? Well, I, uh...
[MISATO]
Sasahara's that way.
[BOTH gasp]
[KOUJIROU]
Here you are.
I saw him feeding his goat this
one time in the pouring rain
and I thought that
was pretty nice.
Yeah, I get it!
That does sound pretty
nice. Mm-hmm, mm-hmm!
I see why you like him.
What? I never said
I liked him or anything
just because he's nice.
[WEBOSHII]
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm! So anyway!
Tell us who you're after!
Huh? What do you mean?
If you like someone,
then tell us who it is.
[FE] Um, I can't think
of anyone in particular
that I'm interested in.
I guess I'm just not into
weirdos like you guys are.
[FE screams]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
[JUDO FIGHTER 21A, 21B pant]
--Begin!
--Seiya!
[JUDO FIGHTER 21B grunts]
Here I come!
[JUDO FIGHTER 21B screams]
Soiya!
[REFEREE 21A]
One point!
[sighs]
[BOY 21A groans]
[BOY 21A]
Ow! Man, that hurts.
[GIRL 21A]
Hang on a sec. Here.
Thanks, I really
appreciate it--[gasps]
What's wrong?
Lemme see your hand.
Huh? [gasping]
[CROWD chattering]
[sighs]
[TAKASAKI]
It's finally my day off,
but since I have so
many errands to run,
this will end up being just as
busy as a regular work day.
Oh, well. At least
it's peaceful.
I guess that's enough.
It looks like this'll be another
boring day for me, then, huh?
Hello there.
[TAKASAKI]
Hm?
Casual clothes?
This is what she looks
like outside of work?
Are you out shopping
as well, Mr. Takasaki?
[TAKASAKI]
And those pigtails!
Bumping into Sakurai
like this on a weekend?
It's almost as if we're
more than just colleagues.
[TAKASAKI whimpers]
I'm so happy.
This is the best day ever.
Oh, no, are you okay?
You're not feeling ill, are you?
[TAKASAKI gasps]
Don't worry about me!
I'm surprised to see
you here, that's all!
Oh! Could you be out shopping
today, too, Ms. Sakurai?
Yes! There's a great sale
on green onions today,
so I figured I'd go
out and pick some up.
Green onions, huh?
Well, if you ever find yourself
needing bamboo sprouts,
just give me a shout
and I'll get you some!
Uh, you have extra
bamboo sprouts?
[TAKASAKI]
Well, I kind of have...
You know, come to think of it...
[IZUMI]
Really, you do?
That sounds wonderful!
[TAKASAKI] Bumping into her
like this on the weekend...
It feels like it
was meant to be.
[TAKASAKI] Almost as if
fate brought us together.
This wasn't some chance
encounter. It was destiny.
I never believed in this
kind of stuff before,
but I think I get it now.
[TAKASAKI groans]
I wish I were a green onion!
You sure you're okay?
It kind of looks like
you're in pain, so...
...maybe we should sit down.
[TAKASAKI gasps]
Don't worry about me!
I'm doing completely
fine, 100 percent fine!
I wouldn't want you to trouble
yourself with something like--
[IZUMI]
...maybe we should sit down.
[gasps] With something like...
[IZUMI]
...maybe we should sit down.
[TAKASAKI gasping]
[IZUMI]
...maybe we should sit down.
[TAKASAKI gasps]
[IZUMI]
...maybe we should sit down.
[whimpers]
[TAKASAKI]
This is the best.
I hope it never ends.
[TAKASAKI] I know! I have a
great idea, Ms. Sakurai!
There's a park a
few blocks down,
so why don't we go down
there and sit down?
[IZUMI]
Uh, okay!
[TAKASAKI]
Oh, man.
I can't believe this is
actually happening right now.
[TAKASAKI gasps]
Hang on!
Could this be...
considered a date?!
[gasps]
[TAKASAKI]
Why is she here?
[TAKASAKI] Actually,
you know what? I'm fine!
So maybe we should
just turn around.
[TAKASAKI]
A student, here? Now?
I can't have her
seeing us together.
Uh... Hey! What are you
two doing over there?
[TAKASAKI]
D-Don't be silly!
This is just a completely
casual meeting between adults.
And, uh, that's it!
Fancy seeing you here!
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you two were on a
secret date or something.
If you think it's a secret,
why would you say it out loud?
[YUUKO]
Aw, what's the big deal?
You guys look like
you're having fun!
[TAKASAKI]
You turd.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Uh--hm?
I hope you're having a fine
morning today, Ms. Sakurai.
Huh?
Look, it's the two love birds!
Look at 'em blush!
Ooh!
That's enough!
No teasing the teachers!
[TAKASAKI sighs] Those darn kids
always take things too far.
I'm sorry about all this.
I hope it didn't cause
you too much trouble.
[IZUMI]
It didn't.
But, um...
I, um, thought it
was kinda cute.
That's it! Okay! Let's do this!
[TAKASAKI]
What's wrong with me?
It would never work out
so perfectly like that!
I gotta get outta here!
What's going on?
Nothing!
Why does it look like you're
hiding something, Mr. Takasaki?
[TAKASAKI gasping]
Well, it's been a
lovely coincidence
seeing you here, Ms. Sakurai!
And wouldn't ya know it,
there's a student here, too!
What are the chances
of seeing two people
from the school in
the exact same place!
Hm? What was your name?
It's Aioi, isn't that right?
Just kidding!
Of course I'd remember!
Uh--
[TAKASAKI]
Well! In any case!
I've got places to go
and people to see,
so if you'll excuse me, I'm
gonna hit the 'ol dusty trail!
[YUUKO gasps]
[TAKASAKI sighs]
[TAKASAKI] Maybe... I should
pick up some green onions.
[WOMAN 21A] Sorry for
calling you out like this.
[MAN 21A]
You sleep okay last night?
[WOMAN 21A] I did, but...
I had the most peculiar dream.
[MAN 21A]
Oh, really? What happened?
[WOMAN 21A] Well, um...
we were standing here kissing.
[MAN 21A] What if I made
that dream a reality?
[gasps] Hey! Uh, Hakase!
Let's go get you
some more snacks!
[WOMAN 21A] Do you really have
those kinds of feelings for me?
[MAN 21A]
Save your questions for after.
[WOMAN 21A]
Oh, my! Sir!
[WOMAN 21A moans]
[NAKAMURA] After one whole
month of investigating,
I've determined
that Nano Shinonome
visits the supermarket in
this district every Saturday.
If my calculations are correct,
she'll be arriving soon.
And once she does,
I'll be right behind her.
When I find my opening,
I'll call upon my trusty
friend, Mr. Short Circuit,
once again to assist
me in this abduction.
For science!
It's the perfect plan!
Today shall be the day I
study you, Miss Shinonome!
[NAKAMURA]
Or not!
Why isn't she showing up?
Could it be that she doesn't
come to the supermarket
every week?
Maybe my calculations were off.
[grunts] No. I can't
give up now.
I've already waited this long,
so I can't let it
be for nothing!
[TAKASAKI]
Hmm.
I knew it! So it is
you, Ms. Nakamura.
Fancy seeing you here.
[NAKAMURA] Likewise,
you walking pair of sideburns!
Uh, hello there.
[TAKASAKI]
I hardly recognized you
without your usual lab coat on.
[NAKAMURA]
I don't have time for this
pointless small talk right now.
If I don't focus,
Nano Shinonome might
slip through my fingers
without me even noticing her.
I never woulda guessed
that your street clothes
would be so boy-ish.
I'm surprised.
It looks pretty cute on you.
[NAKAMURA gasps]
Um, well, no, actually,
this is just my, uh...
I'm so used to you being all
serious with that lab coat on,
so seeing you like this makes
you seem cuter, I guess.
[NAKAMURA]
I'll have to retreat for today!
Hang on, you forgot
your science thingy!
So then,
have you given any
thought to what you might
want to do in the future
at all, Miss Minakami?
I have thought about it.
[IZUMI gasps]
Uh... So, are you planning
on finding a job?
[gasps] Then... are you...
looking into higher education?
[whines] Uh...
'Kay that means...
[IZUMI gasps]
I think I get it.
[SOLDIER 21A]
Hey, you find it yet?
It's no good.
We can't find the cube.
[SOLDIER #14]
I thought we stored that thing
somewhere safe.
How could it just disappear?
Well, look on the bright side.
There's gonna be
a huge cash reward
for whoever finds
the dang thing.
[SOLDIER #22] I'd say
that's worth all the trouble
we're going through.
[SOLDIER #0]
Ha, yeah!
If we can find one,
then we can find the other.
Better keep looking.
[SOLDIER #8] If I could just
get my hands on that cube.
I wonder if that would help me
get in the King's good graces.
[SOLDIER #14]
Hey, uh, who's that?
Over there?
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
[MIO]
My wooden cube.
Give it back.
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
Hey, now.
What seems to be the big
problem here, little girl?
How did you manage
to get on this ship?
Don't tell me.
You're some kind of stowaway?
Do you know how we punish
kids for doing that?
We throw them
straight into prison.
Ten years minimum.
And the worst part is,
I'd be your warden!
That what you want?
[SOLDIER #22 groans]
No, 22!
Damn it! You're gonna pay!
[SOLDIER #22]
Hold it. I can handle this.
I got careless for
a split second there.
But I've got this under
control now, trust me.
I gotta say.
You sure do pack
quite a powerful punch
for such a tiny girl.
Now then.
This has been fun,
but it's time you
started talk--[groans]
[SOLDIERS scream]
[SOLDIER #14]
Is he okay?
[SOLDIER #8]
Negative. He's dead.
She's a monster!
The stowaway isn't gonna stop
until she gets the wooden cube!
Let's charge at her together!
We've got her outnumbered.
[OFFICER]
Hmm.
--[SOLDIERS gasp]
--There's no reason to panic,
now that I'm here,
so everybody can settle down.
[SOLDIERS]
Officer!
[OFFICER] Relax. Just sit back
and watch how it's done.
[SOLDIER #8]
In this situation,
the Officer might
actually be our only hope.
[OFFICER]
Hmm. So, she's on a solo mission
to claim the wooden cube.
Undoubtedly a highly-skilled
agent sent by an unknown enemy.
All that skill and power
could be quite useful, though,
if we can convince her to
switch over to our side.
Fortunately, I am in possession
of the other wooden cube.
It's what she wants,
so it makes the perfect
bargaining chip,
and we should be able
to come to an agreement.
[OFFICER] I just happen to have
the cube you're looking for,
so what do you say
we make a trade?
We could strike a
promising deal--
Ooh!
[SOLDIERS]
Officer!
[SOLDIER #8]
He's dead, too!
[SCHOLAR]
This is not good!
[SOLDIER #98] She took down the
Officer like it was nothing!
[SOLDIER #14]
We'll show you!
We're not gonna let you
out of here alive!
[SCHOLAR]
This is bad! Really, really bad!
By definition,
that means it's not good.
What does that mean, Scholar?
How bad is "really, really bad"?
[SCHOLAR gasps] If you would all
stop yelling at me for a moment
and observe the intruder's head,
you'll notice that she has
a wooden cube in her hair.
And if you look on the
other side of her head,
there's another wooden cube.
Meaning that she has a
total of two wooden cubes!
Which means that she has both
wooden cubes in her possession!
--[SOLDIERS gasp]
--But even if she has
both the cubes,
we should be fine as
long as she doesn't know
how to summon the
ancient weapon.
That's right!
We can still win if--
--Shut up and listen to me!
--[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SCHOLAR] It says here
in the Hell Encyclopedia,
that whoever possesses
both of the wooden cubes
will be bestowed with
the unstoppable power
of the ancient weapon!
In other words,
it means that whoever possesses
both of the wooden cubes
will be bestowed with
the unstoppable power
of the ancient weapon.
What does that mean?
Explain that once more, please!
Yeah, I didn't get
it the first time!
In other--
--[explosion]
--[SOLDIERS scream]
There's no time to explain!
It is over!
If we try to fight here,
not only will we be doomed,
but the entire world
along with us!
[SOLDIERS gasping, murmuring]
[CAPTAIN]
Don't you dare back down!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Never run from you fears!
Conquer them!
It's the Captain!
Captain!
All right!
[CAPTAIN]
Listen. Trying to attack her
head-on one at a time will
only guarantee your demise.
It would be futile.
However! The enemy
is but one lone girl!
So we have the advantage
of numbers on our side!
We must work together
as a complete unit
to rush in and take those
wooden cubes from her
no matter the cost!
I'll take point and
lead the vanguard!
Attack!
[gasping]
[SOLDIERS]
Captain!
[CAPTAIN]
Forget about me! Carry on!
But, we can't just--
[CAPTAIN]
You piddling maggot!
I don't remember
training a pathetic,
cowardly soldier like you!
[growls]
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH scream]
[SOLDIER #8]
It's all over.
The Officer is gone.
The Captain is stuck in a hole.
What hope do we have left now?
[SOLDIER #82]
We're a team.
And we still have each other.
[SOLDIER #82] One for
all... and all for one!
[SOLDIER #82 yelling]
[SOLDIER #82 screams]
[CAPTAIN whimpering]
[CAPTAIN screams]
[SOLDIERS]
Captain, no!
[SOLDIER #8] It's been 12 long
years since I joined this squad.
[SOLDIER #8] Over a decade
of my life gone in a flash,
because of this girl.
[SOLDIER #8]
It can't be over.
I'm not done yet.
It won't end like this!
[gasps, sighs]
[SOLDIER #8 groans]
[SOLDIERS crying]
[SOLDIER #95]
We're doomed!
Please, no!
I don't wanna die here!
[SOLDIER #64 whimpering]
[gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[screams]
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
I'll go stand in the hallway.
[SAKAMOTO]
Huh?
That's so obvious!
Whatever.
I've got nothing else
to do right now,
so I might as well
indulge the little brat.
[SAKAMOTO screams, whimpers]
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
Making something a waste of time
is a special talent indeed.
[NAKAMURA]
Hmm.
Oh, you have bed-head.
It's actually
pretty cute on you.
[NAKAMURA groans]
It looks pretty cute on you.
[NAKAMURA whines]
[NAKAMURA groans]
[NAKAMURA]
What the hell am I doing?
What's wrong with me?
[NANO humming]
I'm finished now!
The bath is all yours
whenever you--[gasps]
[BOTH snoring]
[NANO giggles]
[WOLF 21A howling]
[UMBRELLA]
I'm a Love Umbrella.
If you need a matchmaker,
I've got you covered!
Write your name on one side,
and your special
someone on the other.
Oh? You don't have one?
Then for a sad sap like you,
the next My Ordinary Life
is Episode 22.
Look forward to it!