[YUUKO]
I'm telling ya,
Daiku Coffee is pretty great
after that remodel they did.
[MIO]
Really?
[YUUKO]
See? Check it out!
[MIO]
You weren't kidding.
It's like a real café now.
[TAMAMURA]
Welcome!
[YUUKO]
I've already been here,
but take as long as you need to
figure out their menu and order.
[MIO]
Oh, really? Okay.
[YUUKO chuckles]
Yeah, lemme get a white
chocolate mochaccino
in a grande, please.
[YUUKO]
Huh?
[MIO] And if it's not too much
trouble, can I get it with
caramel sauce, hazelnut syrup,
extra whip, chocolate chips,
and an additional shot of
espresso, affogato style?
[YUUKO]
Screw this!
[MIO]
Wait! Where are you going?
[NAKAMURA] My previous attempts
at researching Nano Shinonome
were unsuccessful.
But luckily, I have a plan!
Now with double the
oxidizing strength,
unleashing the power of oxygen,
it'll make my tough problems
disappear like magic!
It's Mr. Oxidation Plus!
With this, I'll finally have
my chance to study that girl!
For the sake of science!
I don't even know what
I wanna study first!
There are so many options.
Maybe I'll start--
[OOGO]
See what you can muster!
[NANO]
Oh, no. What do I do?
Whoa. I guess we're working with
these compass things today.
It looks like you're pretty
excited to get started, huh?
Uh, sure!
[MIO]
Hey, guys!
Today's class is
a study hall now.
[YUUKO]
Yeah! All right!
I wonder if it's because
Ms. Nakamura collapsed again.
[YUUKO] She sure does fall
over a lot, doesn't she?
[NANO sighs]
[MISATO]
Hey, Sasahara!
You're supposed to
be on cleaning duty!
I completed the sweeping
responsibilities assigned to me.
Uh! But you left a pile
of crap on the floor!
[KOUJIROU]
Hm. Did I really?
[MISATO] Go back downstairs
and finish it up!
I'm curious as to how you
knew that you would be able
to find me on the roof.
[gasps]
Don't be stupid!
It's a nice day so I came
to enjoy the warm weather,
and you just happened
to be up here, okay?
I see.
Sorry for troubling you.
I appreciate you always
looking out for me.
[KOUJIROU]
Hm.
[MISATO] Don't you dare
take it the wrong way!
It's not like I did it
for you or anything!
[KOUJIROU]
Wow.
[NANO, MIO gasp]
[YUUKO]
It's my day off!
I've got plans to meet up with
Mai in the next town over.
She said that there would be
free candy involved if I came,
so how could I say no?
[WOMAN A]
Want some bread?
Oh, no thank you, it's fine.
I ate earlier, so--
[YUUKO] I thought dogs were
like, not allowed on trains.
[YUUKO]
Here.
I'm quite all right.
Look, my stop is coming up,
so I better hop out of my seat
right now and get ready to go!
[YUUKO yelps]
[ANNOUNCER A] The next stop
is Tokisadametonyamachi.
[YUUKO]
Good call, Mr. Announcer man!
[ANNOUNCER A] We've now arrived
at Tokisadametonyamachi...
[YUUKO]
Perfect. Get me off this thing.
So long train-riding
people. Yuuko out.
[YUUKO]
This is fine!
I'm just taking longer
for dramatic effect!
[chuckling]
[YUUKO]
I gotta keep my cool!
Once I'm off the train,
this'll all be over!
I'm so sorry! I wasn't looking
where I was going and--
[screams]
[YUUKO]
Come on! Don't sweat it!
I'm in the next town over,
and it's practically a
different country here!
I'll never see any of these
people ever again,
so it's totally fine!
[YUUKO] Is it just me
or am I being followed?
I'm just imagining things!
It's pro'bly 'cause I'm still
flustered from earlier.
Things will be fine
if I focus on getting
to the Daiku Burger place.
Where ever that is.
Well, according to the
map Mai gave me...
...this thing is
nothing but treble.
I'll just ask for
directions. Yeah.
'Scuse me, but do you know how
to get to Daiku
Burger from here?
Ah! Okay! That's it! You better
stop following me around
or I'm gonna report you for
breaking some sort of law!
I'm sure I can find one!
I heard you're looking for
the Daiku Burger nearby.
I'm actually meeting
somebody there,
so I can show you the way
if you need some help.
[EMPLOYEE A]
Welcome!
[YUUKO]
Hm?
[MIHOSHI]
Sorry, Sis. Club ran long today.
You're late!
[YUUKO] Looks like she
was telling the truth.
[EMPLOYEE A]
Thank you for your patience!
[YUUKO] I don't see Mai,
so I guess she isn't here yet.
[YUUKO]
Aw, man.
This has been a day, and
it's barely even started!
Oh, well. At least
I'm in a different city.
Yeah! I just need to
look at the bright side!
I'll learn from what
happened here,
so I can be prepared
for when it matters!
That's right!
If I can survive this
level of humiliation,
I can take on anything
the world throws at me!
[MAI]
Yuuko.
Sorry I'm late.
Wait, what? Is that
what I think it is?
[MAI]
Trick or treat.
[YUUKO] I'm already in this
deep. Might as well commit.
I'm all in!
Trick or treat to you, too.
Don't they know
Halloween was last week?
[CHILDREN] "The Life of
Crow"! Check it out!
[CROW A cawing]
[YUUKO growling]
I'm not sleepy enough
to sleep right now.
[SAKAMOTO] You could always
try counting sheep
in your imagination.
I've heard that helps.
Okay, I'll try
counting sheepies.
One sheepy jumping over a fen--
[SAKAMOTO]
She fell asleep after one?
Wow, that really works!
Let me try!
One fluffy sheepy--
[SAKAMOTO] That sheepy
never made it over.
There ya go.
Thanks a lot!
You're the best, sis.
Hey, so does that
Sasahara guy teach you
how to do stuff like this?
What makes you
think that?! Huh?
Why would I ever go to a guy
like that to teach me anything?
I just thought you
two seemed close, so--
Well, we're not close,
like, at all!
And don't you dare think
that we are! You got it?
[MIHOSHI]
Uh, sis, you're scaring me.
But if you two aren't close,
then why did you iron
his handkerchief?
Uh, that was just something
I found on the ground
and wanted to fix up a little.
[MIHOSHI]
Did you wanna make it nice
because it was Sasahara's?
Yeah, right.
I would never do that.
I felt like practicing my
ironing, and the iron
just so happened to be
out and ready to use
and the handkerchief I
found also just happened
to be sitting underneath it.
I guess.
Yeah! It was just circumstance!
[MIHOSHI]
Dang. She's so transparent.
[MIHOSHI] That doesn't explain
why you looked so happy
ironing something you
found on the street.
There's a simple
explanation for that!
It... was because...
It's because the Earth must've
entered the Photon Belt
at that moment and
reality shifted.
[GIRL A] You'll never
guess what happened!
[GIRL B]
Yeah? What?
[GIRL A] I finally talked
to Oono yesterday!
Wow! Really?
[WOMAN B] Two hours by train.
And one hour by bus.
[WOMAN B] I left behind
the hustle of city life.
In its place, I now
have the peacefulness
of S Town's countryside.
[WOMAN B]
I searched for so long,
never thinking for a moment
that I would actually be able
to find it again.
Yet I never wavered.
I continued my quest for
that one special book.
It brought a spark of color and
excitement into my heart
when I was a child.
Coloring the gray,
uneventful days of my youth.
This is the place. The library.
[WOMAN B] At last...
I can see it once more.
[WOMAN B]
Fate was kind enough
to bring me and
this book together.
And fate has my thanks.
[WOMAN B] While trying to
ignore my racing heart...
...slowly...
[WOMAN B]
...I open up the cover.
Time's almost up,
so finish what you can,
and don't forget to put
your name on the top
before you turn it in.
Ten, nine, eight, seven.
Uh?
Six... Five...
And four... And three...
Two...
And one...
[chuckles]
Zero!
Okay. Everybody pass your
papers up to the front.
[WIFE A chuckles]
You do know that Halloween
is over already, right?
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
Gross! I wanted to
like this coffee,
but it's not very coffee-y.
You wanna run that one by me
again? It's not coffee-y?
I can't really think
of any other way
to explain how it tastes!
It's simply not coffee-y enough!
Here, try it and you'll
see what I mean! Come on!
Okay. I don't see the big deal,
it's just coffee, right?
[gasps]
[GIRL E]
It's not coffee-y enough.
[BOTH]
Hop! Hop! H--!
[HAKASE]
Hop!
[NANO]
[HAKASE]
Hop!
[NANO]
[HAKASE]
Hop!
[BOTH giggle]
[HAKASE] Hey, guys! I finally
finished my latest project!
Look, Biscuit #2!
I'm Biscuit #2.
Oh. It's that thing.
[BISCUIT #2]
Okay. Ouch.
Come on! Don't ignore
him like that!
Um, but I've already
seen this one before.
He's not a "one," he's a "two,"
and that's different!
He's way cooler than before!
Sure.
[BISCUIT #2]
My name is Biscuit #2.
I was made by Hakase Shinonome,
and I'm a biscuit robot!
As my name implies,
I run solely on biscuits.
Biscuits are like fuel.
They give me life.
Hakase, I require
a biscuit at once!
Wha...?
But this is the last one
and I wanna eat it.
[BISCUIT #2]
Huh?
Biscuit #2's special
skill is speed reading!
Check it!
I'm finished.
[BOTH]
Done.
[SAKAMOTO]
Uhh...
Why aren't you excited, Nano?!
Well, it's just that
I can speed read also.
[HAKASE] Then how come
you always read so slow?!
Explain that!
Um, I enjoy taking
my time with books.
It makes me feel like
I'm reading them
like a normal person!
[HAKASE whispering]
Yawn.
Now what seems to be
the problem, Biscuit #2?
Looking at all of
these tiny letters
is kinda making me sleepy.
[HAKASE] That's how a
normal person reads.
[HAKASE yelling]
Why don't you ever
say how amazing I am
when I do all this
awesome stuff?!
Oh, wow, I had no idea it
would make you that upset.
[HAKASE]
I'm not upset, you are!
If it helps, I've always
thought what you do
is pretty impressive.
[gasps]
I'm pretty impressive,
but you don't have to make
such a big deal out of that.
[NANO]
I don't know if I'm the one
that's making it a big deal.
[HAKASE]
Okay!
So tell me more about
how impressive I am!
You're as impressive
as a mountain range!
[HAKASE] I don't know what
that means, so try again.
[NANO] 'Kay. You have an
incredibly vast knowledge!
[HAKASE]
Like it's big? As big as what?
[NANO]
How 'bout as big as a whale?
[HAKASE]
Oh, I like the sound of that!
[NANO]
Whales are pretty big, huh?
[HAKASE]
They're the biggest!
[NANO, HAKASE laughing]
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR] Never say
something is good enough.
Never say "this is good enough."
"That's good enough."
[SOLDIER A]
So, what do you plan on doing?
Play a board game!
What's your act gonna be?
I'm doing an exciting,
yet intellectually
stimulating, quiz game!
Entertaining the princess
for prize money
seems like a great way
to pass the time,
and it can end up
being kinda fun.
Feels nice to enjoy ourselves
and take a break from
all the serious stuff.
Yeah! For sure.
[SOLDIERS gasping]
I'm sure you all thought you
knew where the ball was.
[SOLDIER #66]
But in reality, it's under here.
Not bad, #66!
That's quite the hidden
talent you got goin' there.
Heh. To be honest,
my dream is to become
the Royal Magician someday.
I'd say that dream might
become a reality soon!
I hope so!
All right! I'm getting pumped!
Let's get this thing
started already!
[OTSUKI]
Men! The time has come!
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[OTSUKI]
Silence!
We'll now proceed in the order
indicated by the slips you drew.
Whoever drew one, come forward.
That would be me!
[SOLDIER #16]
Whoa, #66 right off the bat!
Looks like this will
start with a bang.
[SOLDIER #8]
The Royal Magician, huh?
Embrace your dreams, 66!
Now, go ahead and guess
which cup has the--
[SOLDIER #66 screaming]
[SOLDIER #66] I just wanted
to be a Royal Magician!
Next.
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Whoever drew two, step forward!
[SOLDIER #4]
My turn now.
It's time to show the
world what I can do!
I'll make a name for
myself right here!
[SOLDIER #56]
Hey. Who's that?
[SOLDIER #8] It's him, Funny 4!
If anyone can do it, he can!
[SOLDIER #4]
I am #4, here to entertain.
[SOLDIER #4 grunting]
[yells]
[SOLDIER #4 screaming]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Next.
I can't believe 4 failed.
Hey, you doin' all right?
I'm up next.
Huh? Wait, aren't
you the quiz guy?
[SOLDIER #6]
I'm so screwed.
But I don't have a choice.
The quiz game's all I've got.
But if I make it easy enough,
maybe it'll appease the princess
and I won't fall to my doom.
It'll be fine.
As long as she gets
the answers right...
I'll just give her simple,
easy-to-solve questions.
[SOLDIER #6] Uh, #6! And I'm
here to give you a quiz!
Can you name something that has
the word "bread" in it
but is also inedible?
Uh, it's a multiple
choice question!
Uh, The first option
is breadbox
and the second option
is melon bread!
[SOLDIERS]
Wow, that's easy!
Ah!
[grunting]
I give up.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
That is... the correct
secret answer!
[SOLDIER #6] My whole life,
I regretted nothing.
[SOLDIER #6]
Except this!
We're so dead.
Even the quiz master
was sent packing.
[STARLA]
Next.
[SOLDIER #7]
Um, I'm #7!
And I can recite every location
the Olympics have ever taken--
[SOLDIER #7 screaming]
[SOLDIER #8] We'll never
forget your courage, #7.
What's the matter?
Is no one here capable of
entertaining the princess?
[SOLDIER #8]
What am I gonna do?
And here I thought a
cheerleading routine
would be a good idea.
[SOLDIER #0]
Speak for yourself!
I was splitting chopsticks
with my butt cheeks!
[SOLDIER #39] I was gonna
dance with a sushi mat!
[SOLDIER #91] I thought I'd
be cool to shred a cabbage!
[ALL groan]
[SOLDIER #8] We're all doomed.
Every last one of us.
Relax.
You didn't forget that you
have me around, did ya?
Wait! You're the--
His harlequin antics have made
him the best clown in town.
There's nobody funnier
than this guy.
He's... Harlequeen 13!
I'll turn those
frowns upside-down
and put on an unforgettable
show in the process.
Boom!
Hang on a sec, 13!
I dunno what you have
planned, but it's suicide!
[clicks tongue]
Do you honestly think
I would dance Swan Lake
or something stupid like that?
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[SOLDIER #13]
Just watch and learn.
I'll show you why they call
me the Harlequeen 13--
[SOLDIER #13 screaming]
[SOLDIER #15]
Harlequeen 13!
Huh?! Why am I fall--?!
[OTSUKI]
Next, #5.
Don't make me say it
twice! Come on out!
Who drew that one?
Who is #5?
Is that you?
[SOLDIER #5] No! That's just
what it says on my hat!
[SOLDIER B]
Who is it then?
[SOLDIER D]
Not me!
[SOLDIER #8]
Hang on. Aren't you #5?
[SOLDIERS]
Yeah. He's dead.
Number 5 had better
step forward immediately!
What is the hold up?
[chuckles]
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
I knew it!
Next. I don't care
who it is. Just go.
[SOLDIER B]
What do we do now?
[SOLDIER C]
We're all...
[SOLDIERS]
...completely screwed!
We could have a
thousand more men
and it still wouldn't
make a difference!
[SOLDIER #8] I've had enough
of this stupid game!
And I won't watch this anymore!
[screams]
I'll go stand in the hallway.
[FRAPPUCCINO] I'm a white
chocolate mochaccino
with caramel sauce,
hazelnut syrup, extra whip,
chocolate chips on top, and an
additional shot of espresso,
affogato style,
in a grande size!
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 19!
Look forward to it!