[MALE VOICE 19A]
Hellvetica Standard.
My glasses, my glasses,
my glasses, my glasses.
[MAN 19B panting]
My glasses,
my glasses, my glasses.
[MAN 19B panting, gasping]
My glasses, my glasses,
my glasses!
[gasps, yells]
My glasses!
[screams]
My glasses, my glasses, my
glasses, my glasses, my glasses!
Glasses, glasses,
glasses, glasses, glasses,
glasses, glasses,
glasses, glasses!
[MAN 19B screams]
[FE]
I'm feeling crazy,
so watch closely
as I do something
you've never seen me do and
may never see me do again!
I am a victim of
domestic violence!
[FE squeals, laughs]
[FE]
Well? Did I blow your minds?
[MISATO, WEBOSHII] And what are
we supposed to say to that?
[MISATO]
Seems like something you'd do.
[WEBOSHII]
Yeah, I think you would've
done that at some point.
[MISATO] Uh-huh, it was
definitely a "you" thing.
[FE] Well, then the next thing
I do will be totally "un-me"
and completely out of character!
[FE giggles, gasps]
[FE whimpers]
[FE whines]
I tripped and fell!
[MISATO, WEBOSHII] That is
so something she would do.
[BOTH sigh]
Yup. Seems about right.
[NEWBIE 19A]
Daifuku !
Come and get your daifuku here!
[NAKANOJOU'S FATHER]
Sorry, but...
...could you wear this instead?
It's more appropriate.
[NEWBIE 19A]
Come one, come all!
And get some sweet,
sweet daifuku !
[NAKANOJOU'S FATHER]
Sorry again.
Could you try doing
this without talking?
They said it was on sale,
but the price was
higher than before!
Do you think you could maybe
put on a shirt or something?
Are you sulking now?
[NAKANOJOU'S FATHER gasps]
You're not sulking?
Well, then what's the problem?
Um... [sighs]
You can use your words to talk
to me if you really need to.
[STUDENTS chattering]
Here I come!
[pants, sighs]
[MIO grunts]
[YUUKO gasps]
[grunts, gasps]
--Yes!
--I don't think so!
But I jumped on the mat without
touching the bar, so...
Yeah, you made it past the bar.
By going under it!
How many times do I
have to repeat myself?
You have to get over the bar!
[MIO]
Sorry.
I'll do it right
this time, I swear.
[YUUKO] Here, I'll lower
it to make things easier.
Take it nice and slow.
And remember the jumping
form I taught you before.
[MIO]
Okay!
This is it.
I've gotta at least be able
to make it over the bar
when it's that freakin' low.
[MIO grunts]
[MIO] If I can't even pull this
off, everyone'll laugh at me!
[MIO grunts]
[YUUKO gasps]
Did I do it?
[groans]
You ding-dong!
Why can't you do the "thing"
like I taught you?
Do you just not get it?
Well, I can see me doing a
proper Fosbury flop in my head.
Oh, you're flopping all right.
What you're doing is more
like a Fosbury... torpedo!
[MIO gasps]
A human... torpedo.
[YUUKO]
I wouldn't put it like that!
No, wait.
Actually... I think I just did.
I'm not that bad, come on!
Quit joking!
--[MIO laughs]
--But you are that bad!
[YUUKO sighs]
[MIO]
Sorry.
Hey, don't apologize.
I'll be right here to help
you out until you get it.
[MIO gasps]
[YUUKO] You're the one
who's always helping me out
with my homework.
And now it's my
turn to help you!
I'm gonna stay by your
side, no matter what!
[gasps]
Try not to psych yourself out!
Just relax a bit and take
your time with it, okay?
You totally got this thing!
I believe in you, Mio!
[MIO]
I've always been bad at sports,
for as long as I can remember.
[SOCCER PLAYERS laugh, gasp]
I hate to break it to you, Mio,
but you're playing the wrong
kind of football right now!
[MIO] I can be just as
athletic as anyone else.
But, whenever I have
to follow any rules,
everything falls apart!
[MALE TEACHER 19A]
Get ready!
And... fall!
[MIO grunts]
You're supposed to fall
backwards on your back!
[MIO] But... that doesn't
mean I can't change.
I can be better!
I just have to try!
One, two...
There! Huh?
[YUUKO] Mio, you are literally
spinning out of control!
[MIO]
I don't care how long it takes.
I don't care if I keep failing!
[panting]
[MIO] At least there's
one thing I know I can do.
I'll never give up!
[BOTH]
One, two, three!
Well, almost.
Let's try it one more time.
[MIO]
Yuuko believes in me.
I think I'm gonna take
a quick breather, 'kay?
Sure, go ahead.
[MIO sighs]
[MIO]
So, I can believe in me!
[MIO] I'll give it
everything I've got!
I won't quit!
[MIO] I can be better
if I keep on trying!
[yells]
Great effort can take you
to even greater heights.
--[MIO grunts]
--[YUUKO groans]
[BOTH groan]
[YUUKO groans, grunts]
[MIO gasping]
[NARRATOR 19A] And thus,
the "Torpedo Flop" was born.
[CHILDREN]
The Life of White Tigers!
Check 'em out!
Like... All they do is sleep.
And that one in the front
is giving us a good
view of its butt.
[MIO]
Sure is.
They aren't really
doing anything,
so there's not much
else to look at.
[YUUKO] And after all the effort
we made to come out! Rude.
[MIO] I'm just glad
we got to see them.
Yeah.
[YUUKO, MIO]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH squeal]
Wow!
[PYON panting]
[SAKAMOTO sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
It's raining!
I gotta go bring in the laundry!
[SAKAMOTO]
Hey! That's the wrong way!
Huh?
[SAKAMOTO groans]
[SAKAMOTO sighs]
There!
Yay!
Uh--[gasps]
Looks like it's wet already.
[SAKAMOTO]
You should still bring it in!
[NANO whining]
[NANO]
Hakase, Sakamoto, I'm home!
It started pouring
out of nowhere,
so I hope you were
able to get the laundry
before it got too wet.
It's not my fault! Sakamoto
told me to bring it in!
[SAKAMOTO sighs]
[HAKASE]
I'm tellin' ya!
It was all the kitty's idea.
He was the one
that made me do it!
So what you're saying is,
you knocked the laundry over
while Sakamoto was
making you bring it in?
No, he specifically told me to
take the clothes and just--
throw them all on the ground.
[SAKAMOTO]
I did not!
Way to blindside me.
Don't blame someone else
for your messes, kid!
But you said to!
[SAKAMOTO] I never told you
to throw things on the ground!
--Did, too!
--[SAKAMOTO] I did not!
I wish you weren't a liar!
[SAKAMOTO]
I'm what?!
[HAKASE]
Nano.
Why don't we just blame this
whole thing on Sakamoto?
That okay?
[SAKAMOTO]
That is not okay, brat!
No big deal.
I just gotta wash that laundry
again and it'll be good as new.
Oh! Good point! [chuckles]
Guess that's true.
[NANO] But, I'll never get
the time I spend on it back.
[BOTH gasp]
As punishment, neither of you
will be getting dinner tonight.
Aww.
[SAKAMOTO] Dammit.
I didn't do anything wrong!
But it was only
Sakamoto's fault!
See? He said so himself!
He confessed!
So you can blame him!
[SAKAMOTO groans]
[NANO]
All right, then.
Since he owned up
to his mistakes,
the only one that doesn't
get dinner is you.
--[HAKASE gasps]
--[SAKAMOTO chuckles]
Wait! I wanna take
some of the blame!
And I can own up
to my mistakes, too!
Like how I was the
one who tried to
bring in the laundry
in the first place
and accidentally knocked it over
and got it all wet--[gasps]
[NANO]
Ta-da!
We'll be having special
rice omelets for dinner!
Wow!
The eggs were on sale today!
Wait. I thought I wasn't
allowed to have dinner.
[NANO gasps]
Yeah, you're right!
I completely forgot about that!
Well, um... then...
I guess I can let you have
the rice omelette for tonight!
--[SAKAMOTO sighs]
--Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
--But tomorrow, you get nothing!
[HAKASE groans]
[NANO, HAKASE]
♪ Swim, swim! ♪
[NANO]
♪ Shark, shark, chomp! ♪
[HAKASE]
[NANO, HAKASE] ♪ That is
what a shark does best! ♪
[YUUKO]
Mio! Mai! Selamat pagi !
Man, wasn't that clay
self-portrait assignment
a huge pain in the butt?
[MIO gasps] Wait, that
project was due today?
[YUUKO] Look at that!
The great, all-knowing Mio
finally forgot about her
homework for once!
Ugh! I thought it was
due tomorrow! [gasps]
Mai, did you do
your self-portrait?
Ah, dang it.
So, even Mai forgot about it!
You don't see that
every day! [laughs]
Can you not laugh
at this disaster?
But I guess you can say
that when it rains,
it pours.
[YUUKO]
It really...
[MIO]
...started pouring.
[bells chime]
[MONK 19A gasps]
Why you little!
What the hell have you
three done to my temple?
You must be thieves!
Well, not on my watch!
[gasps, yelps]
That was too close!
[MONK 19A]
This must be a curse!
You brought evil
spirits to this place!
[MONK 19A whimpering]
Just get out of here.
Leave this temple now!
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
"We should probably go,"
is what the three girls thought,
while being pelted by
the late autumn rain.
[MAKOTO sighs]
[clanking]
[MAKOTO grunts]
[DAIKU gasps]
[MAKOTO]
I'm beggin' you, Pres!
I'm about to have a
match with Mr. Takasaki
and we need to find someone
to be the referee!
Referee for a Go+Soccer match?
[MAKOTO] That's right.
And if I can beat him,
Mr. Takasaki said that he would
become the club's advisor.
I'll win. Trust me!
But how am I supposed
to know what to do?
Don't worry.
Just read through that
rulebook I let you borrow.
As long as you do that, then
everything is gonna be fine!
[DAIKU]
I have no idea what's going on!
Well, I didn't even
open the rulebook,
so I guess I shouldn't
be surprised.
But still!
What are they doing?
Is this Go+Soccer?
[OGI] You wouldn't get it,
even if you read the rulebook.
[DAIKU gasps]
Ogi!
They're using
forbidden techniques
most advanced players
don't know!
They've reached a level
that defies all theory!
[DAIKU gasps]
[OGI] Observe his stance
with the outstretched arm,
and how it represents the
left leg of a Go table.
In contrast, his opponent's
stance is the stones.
While it seems
simple at a glance,
notice the ball
between his feet.
It's just a guess,
but I think they're trying...
...to achieve the
brilliance of the sun!
[gasps]
[DAIKU]
Where'd he get all that?
Now I'm even more confused!
[gasps]
--It begins!
--[DAIKU gasps]
[TAKASAKI grunting]
Oh, no!
And, Beloved!
[DAIKU gasping]
Hey, Ogi?
What does that even mean?
--Be quiet.
--[DAIKU gasps]
[OGI]
Can't you feel it?
The intensity between these two?
If they're not careful...
...someone could die.
[gasps] Wait, what?
How would that even happen?
I haven't seen such
high-level play in some time.
It's quite impressive.
No wonder the air feels
so restless right now.
Is that--? This stance.
It can't be!
Unleashing that move
in a friendly match?
He's completely insane!
[grunts] I have no choice.
I can't just stand
by and do nothing.
Father, the fated
day has arrived.
[OGI]
In the name of all that is just,
shed thy light
and become a star!
Ogi Forbidden Referee
School! Secret Technique!
[OGI yells]
[OGI]
Ogi Star!
[BOTH gasp]
[OGI grunts, yells]
This is it!
A final love for all!
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH groan]
[TAKASAKI panting]
You're pretty good.
[MAKOTO panting]
Hey, thanks. You, too.
[DAIKU]
What the heck?
I kinda just started this
little club on a whim.
But now...
...it's gotten crazier
than I could've imagined!
[sighs]
Huh?
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR] I break
down when no one can see me.
[CLAY] Step on me all you'd
like, but I'll never break!
That's right, it's me, Clay!
I can be molded into anything!
But today, I shall take the form
best suited to
battle the children!
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 20!
All right, kids, bring it on!