[YUUKO] I bet she's a total
master at mental math!
Who's a what now?
Nano, the transfer student.
[MIO]
Hm?
A robot like her would
have a calculator function
or something, right?
What're you talkin' about?
There's no way that
she's a robot.
[YUUKO]
Come on, it's so obvious
with that thing
sticking out of her!
Huh? The key in her back is
your only piece of evidence?
You're jumping to conclusions.
Hang on! Just hear
me out on this one.
If she is a robot...
...that'd be dope!
And it'd also be off the chain!
I have no idea what that means,
but you're sure excited.
I think I'm gonna officially
start investigating
to see if Nano is
a for-real robot.
Hold on! Isn't that
going too far?
It's no prob!
I've come up with
a foolproof plan!
[YUUKO]
Oh, Nano?
[NANO gasps]
Yes?
[YUUKO snickers]
Question for ya.
[NANO]
Hm?
What's 3,260 plus 260,
then divided by 320?
[NANO gasps]
Well, uh, if I were to follow
the order of operations, uh...
It sure is a thinker.
[YUUKO coughs]
Maybe you should
calculate this one.
[coughing]
[MIO] You're kidding me!
That was your big idea?
That's a toughie.
If you don't mind, I'd like
to use something special.
[YUUKO]
A bite!
[BOTH]
The line snapped!
'Kay, first things first.
I'll need to start by wiping
the slate completely clean.
[BOTH]
She's legit using it!
[NANO]
Here goes. One, two, three.
[YUUKO, MIO]
She's like... like a...
...like a... She's
a like, a total newb!
[NANO]
All right, take 3,260 and...
[BOTH] What happened
to using the abacus?
[MIO]
Wha--?! Hey, pull it together!
[NANO gasps]
What happened to her?
[MIO]
How you holdin' up?
Don't worry 'bout me.
I just crumbled under the
weight of my ambitions.
I told you right from the get-go
that she wasn't a
robot girl, didn't I?
Any way I can help?
I could offer you a drink?
[YUUKO] This is it!
It's the sacred chalice!
[YUUKO]
Could it be? Show me the oil!
What a soup-prise!
Yuuko!
Oh, guess not. Huh?
Hey there.
[MAI]
Here.
[YUUKO]
She threw a fastball!
[MIO]
Oil?
For you.
Oh! That's so nice.
I appreciate the gesture.
[BOTH gasp]
[YUUKO]
Strike!
You can have this, too.
[YUUKO]
Curveball!
[MIO]
A monkey wrench?!
Wow, thanks a bunch.
I needed one of these.
[YUUKO]
To eat?
Another strike!
[MIO groans]
[MIO]
All right, you two.
I think now's a good time
to chill the heck out.
Can't you see that
she's uncomfortable?
It's skinship.
Yeah, we just wanted
to be friends with you.
[MIO]
Seriously?
There's no way
she'll be your friend
if you keep freaking
her out like that!
[YUUKO]
I'm sorry.
[MIO]
That's better.
Hey! I'm not bothered,
so don't worry.
[MIO]
Huh? You sure?
Oh. That's right! The soup!
I'll help myself if
no one else wants it.
[YUUKO]
Would you look at that?
I guess things
are all good then!
[MIO]
She's obviously...
[NANO]
Did I lose a tooth?
[MIO] If you try putting
yourself in her shoes,
how would you feel?
[MIO]
Cut it out already.
[NANO gasps]
[NAKAMURA]
I need to know.
How did such a highly advanced
technology come to be?
That transfer student
who just started here
has a strange demeanor.
In addition to that bizarre key.
Well, no matter how
you slice it,
she absolutely has
to be a robot.
Why was such an innovative
piece of tech being kept secret?
And why is she attending our
plain little high school,
of all places?
I want to know. I need to know.
For science.
Once I do, that robot
will be mine.
Oh!
Pardon the intrusion,
but I brought the textbooks
you asked me to get,
Ms. Nakamura.
[NAKAMURA]
She came!
Now I must act, posthaste!
All done! If you'll
excuse me, I'll be going.
[NAKAMURA]
One moment, Miss Shinonome!
So, uh, would you like a cup
of coffee before you go?
Huh? No! I would hate
to be a bother!
Oh, come on. Don't be
such a stick in the mud.
You can think of this
as a "thank you."
Here, I just brewed
a fresh beaker.
Get it while it's hot.
One cup won't hurt me.
[NAKAMURA]
Let's see what happens
if I add a little something
to calm her down.
Way down.
For science, of course.
If there are no results,
I'll resort to my trusty
Mr. Short Circuit.
Again, for science.
[NAKAMURA]
Here ya go.
Thanks so much.
It smells really good!
[NAKAMURA grunting]
[NAKAMURA]
Why'd I drink it?
Fight it.
Hang in there!
[NANO] Well, uh,
I'm gonna head out now.
[NAKAMURA]
Wait, come back.
I need to study you...
for science.
Hey. Did ya hear?
Ms. Nakamura the science
teacher passed out.
Oh, wow, she sure does
that a lot, doesn't she?
[BOY F]
Rawr! Rawr!
[BOY G yells]
[sighs]
[NANO]
Today was pretty stressful.
There were one too
many close calls,
but my classmates
seem really nice.
I hope we can all
be friends someday.
[BOY F]
Take this!
Rocket punch!
Ka-boom!
[BOY F yelling]
[BOY G]
Taste my robot's maximum power!
[sighs]
--[BOY F yells]
--[BOY G] Ha-ha!
[NANO]
Hakase! Hakase!
Ah, Nano! Good to have you back!
Huh...? Why did you just
say the same thing twice?
Know what, never mind
that for right now!
I wanted to ask you to
take this key off of me!
Uhh... But why?
What do you mean "why"?
It's negatively impacting
my school life!
I can never sit back
properly in my chair.
Students look at me weird
and one even filmed me!
I've been able to get by so far,
but I don't know
if that'll last.
Ahh.
That key's so cute though.
But can't you see that as long
as I have it stuck on my back,
the other kids are never gonna
treat me like a normal girl?
It'll help make you popular!
I wanna be normal!
And I wanna have an ordinary
high school life, so--
Huh?
[HAKASE yelps]
Why? I never asked to
have these crazy features.
At least my hand didn't
come off at school.
What's the big deal if everyone
finds out that you're a robot?
[NANO] People will think
that I'm not cute
'cause everyone knows
that robots aren't cute.
But robots are the cutest!
They're not even
the littlest bit cute!
They are!
Is this gun barrel cute?
Yeah, it is!
And what about the USB
drive in my big toe?
Adorable!
[NANO] Even the sweet buns
in my forehead?
I said it's cute!
Yeah? I say you're
a mad scientist!
I said it's cute!
[growls]
I just wanna live an
ordinary high school life!
[NANO]
Wow! It's chikuwa !
[HAKASE]
Those sure are tasty!
[MEN chattering]
[MAN F]
Sorry I'm late, fellas.
[MEN chattering]
[HAKASE]
Three. Two. One.
[screams]
[BIRD]
Four o'clock! Four o'clock!
Four o'clock! Four o'clock...
[NANO screams]
[BORD] Four o'clock! Four
o'clock! Four o'clock...
[PART TIMER A]
Hey there! It's me, daifuku !
And I'm cheap!
Get your daifuku here!
Mr. Nakanojou! I hope
you're doing well!
True daifuku don't talk!
[PART TIMER A]
I'm sorry. But I can't help it.
I get so worked up
when I wear this mask!
I put my entire heart and soul--
What did I say about speaking?
[NAKAMURA] Okay. Mistakes
may have been made.
And I might have
taken things too far,
but that's science for you.
I can't underestimate
that robot.
It's gonna take all I have to
bring her in and study her.
Enter Mr. Short Circuit!
My trusty robot disabling device
that's never failed me
'cause I've never used it!
I'm positive that
this'll do the trick.
Or why else would
I call it "trusty"?
[NAKAMURA]
Time is of the essence.
[NAKANOJOU screams]
[NAKAMURA]
Run away!
Uh. Ms. Nakamura?
Hold on! What's this?
You need to you fasten that
top button of yours, mister!
Would you just leave me alone?
I can have it
unbuttoned if I want!
No way! You need to do what
your student counselor says!
[MAKOTO]
Ugh. Seriously?
You're playing the
counselor card?
Yes, I am. Come here
so I can button you.
[MAKOTO] I can do it myself!
Don't embarrass me like that!
[TAKASAKI]
Uh...
What's going on?
I can't count on you to fix it,
so I'll just do it
for you, Mako.
--[gasps]
--[MAKOTO] Hey, back off.
[TAKASAKI]
Wait, "Mako"?
[IZUMI]
Come here.
What are you doing
manhandling me like that?
I said back off!
[IZUMI] Hold still. I'll fix you
up so you can go to class.
[TAKASAKI]
"Manhandling"?!
"I'll fix you up"?
Ugh, cut it out.
Hey, just stop
groping me would you?
[TAKASAKI]
"Groping"?!
[TAKASAKI] What kind of
relationship do these two have?
Well, what do ya know,
problem solved.
'Kay, see ya. Got places to be.
[IZUMI]
Hold on a sec!
Aren't you afraid
everyone'll make fun of you
for being dressed
all sloppy like that?
I'm sloppy?
You're the one who
dresses sloppy
at home all the time, y'know?
[TAKASAKI] "At home"?
Does she wear a-a sloppy dress?
Sloppy dress at home! Oh, yeah!
[TAKASAKI]
Wait, that doesn't make sense!
When would a Chinese dress
ever be considered sloppy?
Am I dumb or something?
How could I possibly be a
teacher and be this stupid?
I've gotta pull myself together!
Think! What's counts as being
sloppy in a normal sense?
[TAKASAKI]
Dressing like this?
Enough! Stop it! You idiot!
Are you finished?
I'm outta here.
You didn't fix your button!
[TAKASAKI gasps]
[CHILDREN] "The Life of Oguri
Cap!" Check him out!
[OGURI CAP grunting]
[TAKASAKI]
You idiot!
Are you finished?
I'm outta here.
You didn't fix your button!
[TAKASAKI gasps]
[TAKASAKI]
I've gotta follow.
[ANNAKA]
Mr. Takasaki!
We found Nakanojou
unconscious on the floor
of the science room!
[TAKASAKI]
Wha--?
[ANNAKA] We need you to
come help like, right now!
--[IZUMI] Hey, wait a second!
--[MAKOTO] Leave me alone!
Okay. Now listen up.
[ANNAKA]
Yeah?
I'm sure Nakanojou's fine!
Huh?!
That's right! He's
probably just napping!
[ANNAKA whines]
But I looked at his eyes
and they're all whited out!
[TAKASAKI]
Wha--?
Fill them in.
[ANNAKA]
Huh?
I'll give it a shot.
[TAKASAKI]
Wha--?
Don't do that!
[ANNAKA]
Huh?
Look over there!
Give me the lowdown
on this business!
It's my sworn duty as a teacher
to stop this kind of
illicit relationship.
It's more important
than, uh, you know.
Get what I mean?
You mean Ms. Sakurai and her
little brother over there?
Let's go.
'Kay?
[TAKASAKI]
Prepare yourself.
There's no time to waste.
After all, I am a teacher.
[ANNAKA]
Hey, it's this way!
[BOTH]
Hop! Hop! H--
Hop!
[BOTH giggle]
[BUS ANNOUNCER A] Next stop:
Tokisadame Station, North Gate.
[BUS ANNOUNCER A]
A stop has been requested.
[STUDENT A laughing]
That's not even close
to your stop, dude!
Yeah, but it's so fun to push
the buttons every time!
[STUDENT A] You pushed
the last one too, right?
[STUDENT B]
And no one even noticed
'cause someone had
to get off anyway!
[STUDENT A] So I guess you're
actually helpin' 'em out then!
[STUDENT B] Oh, look!
Someone needed to get off again!
[STUDENT A]
Hey, you're welcome!
[STUDENTS laughing]
Mom, where'd we put
the daily calendar
with all those tear-off pages?
[YUUKO'S MOM] It should be
in the closet, I think.
[yelling]
[NANO]
Hakase! Hakase!
Ah, Nano! Good to have you back!
Listen! I think it's about time
to take this key off of my back!
It's starting to cause
more and more problems
in my daily school activities!
We did the high jump
in gym class today,
and I could only
belly roll over it!
And during soccer,
I got put on the bench
because I fouled
a kid with my key.
Okay. I can take it.
[NANO]
Splat!
If you were so willing,
you should've told me earlier.
I gotcha. I'll take it
right now if you want.
Not a day goes by
that I don't wish
to have this thing off my body.
But now, I can finally
start my new life
as a normal high school girl!
If you don't mind,
I'd like to get this
key taken right away.
[HAKASE]
Cheese.
Hakase? Don't tell me you're--
I took it.
[NANO]
Plop!
I feel betrayed.
Why?
I thought you meant you
were gonna remove my key,
not take a picture of it!
Oops, my bad.
So, are you ever gonna
take off my key for real?
Let's see.
Hmm...
[NANO]
Kapow!
I've had it up to here
with your silly gags!
Will you do it?
Or will you not do it?
Calm down. I can do it!
I've taken more than my fair
share of keys in my life.
So taking one more key like
yours is gonna be a snap.
[NANO]
Coin, coin, coin, swish!
[laughs]
Wow! I can't believe you
just went "coin, coin"!
And then flew away like "swish!"
Hakase! I have a
question for you!
[HAKASE]
Lemme catch my breath.
I was laughing so hard
I forgot how to breathe.
Listen, I can't help but
notice that I'm making
some pretty strange
reactions today.
You didn't, you know,
do something to me,
did you now?
Well, actually, I gave you a
funny bone feature yesterday!
[NANO]
Shibibi! Shibibi!
Why would you give me such a
bizarre and obnoxious feature?
What is even the
point of it anyway?
I thought it would be funny.
[NANO]
Thump!
Goal!
[NANO]
Dodododo!
--[HAKASE] Mwah!
--[NANO] Bang!
[NANO]
This is it.
This is how I'm gonna die
and it's gonna be awful.
See how much fun we're having?
I'm not having any fun!
All right then.
Forget about the key for a sec
and please just remove
this funny bone feature.
That'll be a hundred yen.
[NANO]
Boom!
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR] This takes
every last ounce of my strength.
[OIL]
I'm oil.
People say I'm slippery,
but I can't really blame them!
That's just who I am.
My boss pours me all the time,
but you're not the boss
of me, so hands off!
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 16.
Look forward to it!