[YUUKO groans]
[MIO]
What's up, Yuuko?
I've got zero motivation.
You serious right now?
But we like, just started
a new semester.
Think of the possibilities.
I'm sure you'll find something
that gets you motivated
if you get the ball rolling.
I can barely roll out of bed,
let alone roll a ball.
How am I supposed to find the
motivation to be motivated, huh?
A motive for motivation. Hm...
How 'bout you just do it?!
'Kay, sure!
[NARRATOR] It must be nice
to be a complete idiot.
[NANO] Hakase! It's about
time to get out of bed!
There we go.
[yawns] Morning.
Whatcha got there?
It's a fish that I'm grilling up
for this morning's breakfast.
[HAKASE]
Fish? But I want a rice omelet!
But you had that for
breakfast yesterday.
Besides, fish are packed with
essential vitamins and minerals.
If you wanna grow up
to be big and strong,
you need to have a
balanced diet. [gasps]
Uh?
[CAT meows]
Um. Excuse me, do you mind
returning our breakfast?
[CAT A grunts]
[gasps] Uh. No, this isn't
what it looks like!
It's definitely not a robotic
component or anything!
You see... It's a...
He's gone!
[NANO panting]
Come back you crazy cat!
Okay, bye...
[panting]
[NANO]
Come to think of it,
what if the cat needs
that food more than we do?
[NANO laughs]
[gasps, screams]
Ahh! Look out!
[sighs]
Hi, good to see ya, Mio!
Selamat pagi !
Oh, hi, Yuuko.
It's nice to see you too.
You think it's okay if I
don't have my student ID?
'Cause I forgot it today.
[YUUKO] Wait, did she miss
that I greeted her in Malay?
[MIO] I hope some upperclassman
doesn't notice and call me out.
If one does, you can just say
you're an upperclassman too,
and they'll have no idea
without your ID.
That won't solve anything.
I guarantee you.
[rumbling]
That sounded like thunder,
but the sky's so clear.
It might start
pouring any second!
It'd suck if we got
rained on outta nowhere!
[groans]
[YUUKO]
It's raining wooden dolls.
[MIO]
Whoa! Are you all right?
[YUUKO]
How does that fall from the sky?
Yeah, that's super weird. I
wonder where it even came from.
I'm just as confused as you are.
But don't worry, I bet
something as crazy as this
only happens once
in a girl's lifetime.
You know. It's like a
freak accident. Right?
[MIO]
Yeah, totally.
That must mean I'm lucky.
[YUUKO]
I'm not lucky at all.
[MIO]
You doin' okay down there?
It happened again with
a red cow this time.
What does it mean?
Y'know, maybe it's not
about luck at all.
Sometimes, bad things happen,
but it could be worse.
At least I wasn't
hit by something
that's disgusting like raw
meat. So, as long as that
doesn't happen,
it's really not that ba--
It's raw salmon!
[MALE STUDENT A]
Good morning!
[MALE STUDENT B]
Oh, heyo!
Morning!
Good morning to you.
Oh, hey. Good morning, Mai.
Selamat pagi !
Good morning.
That looks interesting,
whatcha got there?
This is a real estate magazine.
[MIO] Wha--? Are you
lookin' to buy a house?
[MAI]
Undecided.
[YUUKO] My awesome, unique
greeting gets ignored yet again.
Oh, well. I guess
I have no choice
but to put this short-lived
phrase to rest.
Yuuko.
Huh?
Selamat malam.
[gasping]
Silly Mai! It's
"selamat pagi" ! Ha!
[MIO]
What language are they speaking?
[gasps] It's, uh, time for
homeroom. Take your seats.
Okay, when I arrived
at school today,
I found this inside
my shoe locker.
Now, did one of you kids
put it in there?
Um, well, uh. If you did
do it, that's okay.
I would just appreciate
if you'd own up to it.
Who do you think could've
pulled that kind of prank?
It's pretty bonkers, huh?
How am I supposed to know?
I bet you it was a
student that has like,
a big crush on her or something.
But who would give their
crush a Buddha statue?
Although, I can definitely
understand the feeling
of wanting to give the
person you like a gift,
so I can't really blame 'em.
Oh, that's right.
It's because you have a crush
on that upperclassman
Koujirou Sasahara.
Ah! Don't say it out loud!
[NANO] Where am I?
How did I get here?
[NANO whimpers]
[NANO]
Huh?
I have to get home.
[NANO]
Hakase is probably worried sick.
Plus, I left the grill on,
and that's a hazard.
Oh, no. I can't get down!
Wait. My chopsticks are gone.
And I'm missing a slipper!
What do I do? [gasps]
My hand's gone, too!
Ohh! Now it'll be obvious
that I'm a robot!
[panting]
Ready?
Thanks for the meal.
[MIO]
Hm? Hurry.
You gotta finish eating your
food before fifth period starts.
Wait, all you've got
left is one sausage.
[laughs]
This is all part of my
plan to save the very best
of my lunch for
the grand finale.
That way, I'm for sure
gonna walk away
from my meal satisfied.
[MIO]
Hmm...
And now, without further ado,
it's gonna go down the hatch!
[screams]
[YUUKO growling]
[yelling]
[YUUKO gasping]
[gasps]
Oh!
[screams]
It slipped through!
I got it!
It's done for!
Over my dead body!
[YUUKO]
One... two...
...three... four...
...five!
[MIO gasping]
[STUDENTS chattering]
It's okay!
Uh! It's totally not!
[YUUKO]
Ha, ha! Aw, chill out Mio!
Haven't you ever heard
of the five-second rule?
Haven't you heard of E. coli?!
That is 100% gross!
[MIO]
Uh!
[NAKANOJOU laughs]
Tasty!
[MIO]
She... is such... a moron...
[BOTH] ♪ First comes a rock,
what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors
and a one, two, three! ♪
[NANO]
Aw...
Okay!
[MIO grunts]
[PRINCIPAL]
Good morning, students.
I hope you're having
a wonderful day today.
Now that spring has sprung,
it's time to welcome
a new school year.
But despite the change of
seasons, the cold will stay.
Though I'm sure the cold
will come to a head for me
before it does for you.
[PRINCIPAL laughs]
So please take care that
you don't catch a cold.
After all,
it is my duty as principal
to watch over you students.
But if you neglect to
take my advice to heart,
and you do catch a cold,
well... I'd say you might have
forgotten to respect your
principal's principles.
[PRINCIPAL laughs]
Can I ask you something, Mio?
Make it quick.
We'll get in trouble if
they catch us talking.
Do you think the principal knows
that none of his jokes are funny
to anyone but himself?
It's pretty obvious, right?
You'd think he would take
the hint when no one laughs,
like ever, but it seems like
he's just in his own little
world most of the time.
[MIO] Hm. I never really
thought about it.
[YUUKO]
But wait!
What if he does know
he's not funny,
and he's just trying to
teach the younger,
lazier generation the
importance of persistence?
Possibly.
If that's the case, then the
principal might actually be
some manipulative mastermind!
[gasps]
--[MAI laughs]
--[YUUKO] Mai?
[laughing]
What's her deal?
Don't tell me she's laughing
at those terrible jokes!
Huh?!
[YUUKO] I've never seen Mai
crack up this much before!
She's totally busting her gut!
All right! Here's my chance!
Hey, Mai!
[YUUKO] I can't do it! I want
to tell my own lame joke,
but it'll be too
embarrassing for me!
Yuuko?
[gasps] Huh?
[MAI]
Sorry. Never mind. It's nothing.
[MAI] I think...
I won't say anything.
I'll just leave it where it is.
[MAI laughs]
Next on the docket, we have
a necessary message
from the student counselor,
Ms. Sakurai. You can step up
to the microphone
whenever you're ready.
Umm, I think it's your turn.
It is?!
Excuse me!
I'm Ms. Sakurai,
your student counselor.
But umm. I-I guess you
knew that already.
[IZUMI]
Oh man.
It's so nerve-wracking to be
in front of such a big crowd.
No, I've got to
pull it together!
It's my job to be a model
teacher for my students,
and myself! I'm going
to go ahead and say
what needs to be said!
All right! I've noticed
that there have been some
goats on the school
grounds recently.
Please try your best
to not bring any goats
to school with you
if you can help it.
[SASAHARA]
Goats, you say?
And what is so bad about goats?
[CROWD]
Huh?
I've read the school policies.
Nowhere does it say that we
can't bring a goat to class!
Um, well. That's uh...
[YUUKO] Yo, Mio. Was that
Koujirou screaming about goats?
What? Goats, where?
[IZUMI]
Mm... Then.
I guess goats
are perfectly fine!
[SASAHARA]
Hmph.
[CROWD gasps]
Like hell your goats are fine!
You don't get to make that call!
Even if it's not in the school's
rules, it's still weird!
Duly noted.
But consider this, Misato.
Why should someone like me
be forced to hobble to school
with my own two legs?
I am the eldest son of the
Sasahara household, you know.
I don't give a damn about
your Sasahara household!
You guys are a buncha
normal farmers!
Regardless, that does
not change the fact that
I am the eldest son
of the family.
For real?
Koujirou comes from a family
of ordinary farmers?
And here I thought he was
the greatest of all time.
[MIO] That means the white
goat I saw at the bike rack
must have belonged to Koujirou.
I can just imagine him
riding majestically
atop that beautiful steed
and whisking me away.
A happy new year to me!
[gasps] I do.
[YUUKO]
Whoa!
Uh!
Uh. Also, make sure you
don't use your cellphones
while riding your bikes.
It's extremely dangerous!
And now finally...
I discovered this Buddha
statue that someone put in
my shoe locker this morning.
I just wanted to point out
that pranks like these
are unacceptable!
Excuse us! Coming through!
A Buddha statue...
Ah! Gosh, Mai! Don't stop
like that without warning!
[MAI] There it is again. So
this is what déjà vu feels like.
Uh. Who put this
inside my locker?
I promise I won't be angry
if you own up to it.
We can stand here all day
until someone raises
their hand and confesses.
[CROWD murmuring]
[MALE STUDENT C]
Who actually did it?
[MALE STUDENT D]
Just say it was you.
[PRINCIPAL]
Uhh...
[NAKANOJOU]
Uh?
Uh. Well, I heard it was your
birthday through the grapevine,
so I wanted to
get you something.
[yells]
[PRINCIPAL] Ah, I guess I know
now that a Buddha statue
doesn't exactly
make a great gift.
So. It seems as though
one thought it would be
good to give a present.
But a Buddha statue
is not so pleasant.
Sorry.
[OURA] That concludes
today's assembly.
Thank you for your words,
and we'll all miss you
dearly, Principal.
Vice Principal!
I dunno about you, but staring
at this fire alarm button
makes me wanna push it real bad.
[YUUKO]
Oh yeah, I get that.
[gasps, chuckles]
Why don't you just push it?
I did one time and absolutely
nothing happened.
Oh! Really?
[alarm rings]
--[MALE STUDENT E] A fire?
--[MALE STUDENT F] Seriously?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
What do we do? Book it?
Let's all scramble out
of here as fast as we can!
[MALE STUDENT H]
What do you think you're doing?
Quit pushing me!
[MALE STUDENT I]
You shoved me first, man!
[MALE STUDENT H]
Are you kidding me?
You're really starting
to tick me off!
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Cut it out!
Someone could die if
you start a fight now!
[MALE STUDENT J]
Let's just get out of here.
You can duke it out later!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
[SHINIGAMI]
Excuse me.
--[yelps]
--[SHINIGAMI] Hey.
Sorry, but what does
"being insensitive" mean?
Excuse me!
[screams]
Just what does
"insensitive" mean?
Do you have a moment?
Can you explain what
insensitive means?
[SALARYMAN A]
Somebody help me!
[SHINIGAMI CAPTAIN]
Hey!
[SHINIGAMI]
Oh! Hi, Captain!
Can you tell me
what's insensitive?
Simple. You are.
[TOMIOKA] Attention. Could
Koujirou Sasahara of Class 2-P
please report to Tomioka in
the faculty room immediately.
We understand that it's not
against the school rules.
But really, a goat? Just, why?
I'll ask nicely.
Could you please stop riding
a goat to school everyday?
Why don't you ride a bike?
Mister...
[TOMIOKA]
Tomioka.
Don't forget the mister.
All right, Mister, I'd actually
prefer it if you'd call him
"Koujirou Sasahara,"
and not simply "goat."
[slurping]
Think I'm gonna
stick with "goat."
[NANO]
My name is Nano Shinonome.
I'm just your average robot,
and I live at home
with my creator, Hakase.
[NANO] Hakase spends every
single day inside the house
doing all sorts of really
important research.
And I spend those days
by helping her out
in any way that I can.
Hakase!
I brought you that warm
milk you asked for--
[NANO gasps]
[NANO] I don't have
any special features,
but apparently I'm a robot
that can feel pain.
[HAKASE]
Nano? What's the matter?
Hakase! I stubbed my toe!
The little one!
[HAKASE]
No!
But pinky is the littlest
piggy of them all!
[gasps]
There, I fixed it.
You should feel better now.
[screams]
[NANO] I don't have
any special features,
but apparently my pinky
toe comes off?
Could you tell me what
the key on my back's for?
Oh? Have I never
wound it up for you?
[NANO]
No, you haven't.
But it spins on its
own sometimes.
[HAKASE] Give it a little
twisty-twist, and...
[NANO gasps]
What's going on?
[whistling]
[gasps]
[laughing]
[NANO]
I take it back.
I have all sorts
of special features.
Ya see? Pretty cool, huh?
So, that's it?
That's the only reason
I have a key on my back?
That's right!
It really has no additional
features other than that?
You got it!
Can you take it off?
No!
[NANO gasping]
I wanna leave it on
'cause it looks cute.
[NANO] But I'd really
like it if you took it off.
Aww, it's so cute though.
I just wish that I could be
more like a normal human.
I'd like to sit in a chair
without having to twist weird.
And be able to roll over
in bed when I sleep.
[STUDENTS laugh]
[NANO]
With this thing,
I'll never be able
to go to school.
It would have been better if you
never made me a humanoid robot.
[HAKASE]
Nano...
Huh?
[HAKASE whimpers]
[NANO]
Uhh!
Uh. I'm just kidding.
'Kay? It's a joke.
Stop crying. Please! I'm sorry!
Fine, take it!
Huh?
Take the Akutagawa Prize!
Wait, what?!
[HAKASE]
You heard me!
Akutagawa prize!
You should go get it!
[NANO]
This is my ordinary life.
[MALE STUDENT K]
So, uh. Where am I?
[NANO'S TOE] Hello there!
This is Nano's big toe speaking!
Fun fact: My storage
capacity is one gigabyte.
That's not a whole
lot nowadays, is it?
Next time on My Ordinary Life :
It's the second episode!
Look forward to it!