[rustling]
[CAT meows]
[CAT grunts]
[CAT]
Hm?
[CAT grunts]
[CAT screams]
[YUUKO]
Hey, can I ask you something?
Yeah, of course.
Not that this is
necessarily a bad thing,
but why do you wear those exact
same hair ties every day?
Oh, you mean these?
Hm... 'Cause I wanna.
Sure, but why though?
There's no real reason,
it's just my thing.
Okay...
[MIO gasps, grumbles]
Aw man, I forgot
my math notebook.
Hang on! We have a
math class today?
[MIO] Of course we do! That's
why we had homework for it.
I'm gonna run back
and grab my stuff.
You go ahead!
[YUUKO] Well. I didn't do
that homework, anyway,
so none of this matters to me.
Oh! Hey, Mai!
[YUUKO flubbing]
Selamat pagi !
[YUUKO] Well, well, well,
look who it is!
It's my bestest pal herself!
You've finally come to grace
me with your presence, huh?
You sure do take things to a
whole 'nother level, dontcha?
Y'know! Like a mountain!
Tell me! What's it like being
an actual real-life mountain?
[YUUKO]
Well, I guess she doesn't like
being called a mountain.
[YUUKO]
I get it.
You're mad at me.
And I think I understand why.
Yesterday I stole a bite
of broccoli from your lunch.
The last piece.
And now you're angry.
But don't worry.
I got you a new
thing of broccoli!
You shoulda told me that
you liked it so much
before I shoved it in my mouth!
But we can put all that behind
us, now, 'cause you've got
a new broccoli! So, there
we go. Problem solved!
Anyway, my old man
flipped the channel
just as fast as he could.
[YUUKO grunts]
[YUUKO] It's not about
the broccoli then.
Maybe the cauliflower?
Probably not.
[YUUKO] I've done so many
potentially offensive things,
I don't even know which one
she'd be mad at me for!
[YUUKO] Although, there is one
thing that does stand out.
I'll have to bite the
bullet and apologize.
I don't want her to
stay mad at me forever!
Okay!
Hey, Mai! Listen!
Sorry for eating your main dish!
And for stealing
your apple bunny!
And your rice!
And for leaving the beans!
[YUUKO gasps]
Oh, come on!
Why are you so mad at me?
That's all I can think of!
If it's not your lunch,
then what is it?
[gasps] Maybe it's because of
what happened that one time!
When that Buddha statue
was on your desk.
Is it because I accidently
snapped its head off?
Or that I took it home and did
a crappy job at fixing it?
[YUUKO]
U-Uh!
[YUUKO] Was it because I buried
it and had a secret funeral?
Or because I changed
my mind, dug it back up,
and left a memorial
on your desk?
Or because I changed
my mind again
and decided to
cremate it instead?
Well?
Help me out! I'm dying here!
[music plays]
Ah. Okay, so you were
just listening to music
this whole time.
You couldn't hear
anything, could you?
It's no problem, since I
really was just talking
to myself anyway, so you
didn't really miss much!
[YUUKO]
Man, that was a close one.
I almost spilled every
bean I had to her.
--[MAI] That last part.
--[YUUKO] Huh?
Buddha.
I didn't know.
[YUUKO screaming]
[IZUMI]
Excuse me, Tanaka?
I'm sorry, but do you
have a moment?
Well. Uh.
I just wanted to say that...
It's about your hair.
Don't you think it's getting
a little big these days?
You know what?
Yes?
How 'bout a pancake?
[YUUKO]
Ah, crap!
I totally forgot I had
to do this worksheet!
But I still have five minutes
until class starts.
Mio already let me copy
her work yesterday.
[YUUKO]
I'm begging you!
I can't ask her again!
That means, I have no choice.
[YUUKO]
Hey, uh, Mai?
So, this is totally
embarrassing.
But I kinda, sorta,
completely forgot to do
today's math homework.
Do you think it'd be possible if
I could take the quickest little
peek at yours before
class starts?
[MAI]
Kay.
Oh, wow, really? Thanks!
Just gimme one sec!
I'll have it copied in no time!
[MASAO]
This sucks! I'm so late!
This sucks! This sucks!
[MASAO'S FATHER] Don't make such
a racket in the morning, Masao!
[MASAO]
This sucks!
I'm so frickin' late!
[MASAO'S FATHER] Oh, yeah?
Well, I just got laid off!
[MASAO gasping]
Well, isn't that something.
Sorry Mai, but I think
you might have given me
the wrong paper by
mistake, because...
[YUUKO]
I'll buy you some juice!
Here.
Thanks so much!
[MASAO]
I'm so late for school!
My dad just got laid off!
It sucks for both of us!
--[tiger roars]
--[MASAO screams]
Wait! The heck is that?!
Look behind you, Masao!
You've got way
bigger problems now!
What are you gonna do?
Uh. I mean...
I've got bigger problems!
Why am I getting caught
up in this weirdo comic?!
I can't get distracted!
I'll throw in an extra
snack if you help me!
Here.
[YUUKO] You're the best!
All right, yeah, cool.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
I knew you had it in you.
You didn't have to mess with
me like that, you big tease!
Anyway, time to knock
this thing out!
[YUUKO] I don't even have
today's worksheet. Oh, well.
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
I want to go to New Orleans.
So. Anyone know the solution?
Not a single person?
Mr. Akagi's class is
the worst thing ever.
You get bonked on the head
if you forget your homework,
and get yelled at for
answering a question wrong.
Remember that a lack
of in-class participation
will negatively
affect your grade.
[YUUKO gasps]
[YUUKO] So that's
how he's gonna play it.
Well, it'll take more than
that to trap me, sir!
[AKAGI]
Now, what to do?
I guess since today is
the 23rd, let's go with
the student assigned
to seat number 23.
[YUUKO]
Not me!
[AKAGI]
Nakanojou!
Huh, he's absent?
[YUUKO]
What?!
Ohh! An arm cramp!
[YUUKO groaning]
[YUUKO] Of all times
to be stuck like this.
Oh no, he might actually call on
me now that I can't back down.
I've gotta hide in the blind
spot of his laser eyes.
--Just gonna--
--[rumbling]
[screaming]
[YUUKO]
I'll pretend it was the chair!
Give it a little scoot.
Hey! I think maybe somebody's
phone was just ringing.
[STUDENTS laughing]
Vibrate only!
Let's just hope that they have
a "smart phone."
--[STUDENTS laughing]
--Get it?
Looks like you kids are
in a great mood for math!
Right?
Uh, so, anyway, moving on.
[AKAGI]
Miss Aioi.
[BOTH] ♪ First comes a rock,
what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors
and a one, two, three! ♪
[HAKASE]
Ready!
And lift off!
Woosh!
[NANO]
Why though?
[NANO] Okay. I already
bought sugar and milk,
so I can mark those
off the list.
But I feel like I'm forgetting
something important.
[WOMAN A] Did you see that
insane sale on eggs today?
Yeah, I don't have that much
room in my fridge, but...
Wait that's right!
There was a special on eggs
at the store,
and the sale ends today!
[NANO]
Mm... Do I have enough time?
If I hurry back now,
I think I can make it.
[CAT meows]
[NANO]
Huh?
Aww!
A little black kitty cat!
[meows]
Aww! You're just the cutest!
[NANO meows]
[laughing]
[NANO]
Uh! Hold on.
We can't adopt a cat right now.
I already have my
hands full with Hakase.
Sorry, kitty.
[CAT meows]
I'm back from the grocery store.
Hiya Nano.
[NANO]
Huh?! It's that cat!
I captured the beast!
You can't bring in cats
that you find on the street.
[HAKASE]
What? But he's so cute.
You do have a point.
But he still can't stay here!
Come on!
Don't you think he's cute?
Well, I guess I do. But it's
not about his cuteness.
It's just that, taking care
of an animal can be
a big responsibility. So...
Can you handle it, Hakase?
I can!
Even though you won't be getting
any assistance from me?
That means you're the one who
has to clean his litter box.
You're not gonna
help with anything?
Fine! Then you're not
allowed to pet him ever!
[whimpers] That's not fair!
All right, maybe I can help...
just a little bit.
[CAT sighs]
[gasping] Hakase!
He's napping on my lap!
[HAKASE]
I'm gonna pet him now!
[HAKASE laughing]
[squeals] He's so fluffy!
Huh? Don't hog him!
I want to pet him, too!
His belly is so fluffy!
And his sides are
super fluffy too!
[NANO]
His right paw is extra fluffy!
[HAKASE] And his left paw
is super fluffy too!
His little tail
is the fluffiest!
His tail isn't as fluffy as
this spot behind his ears.
Huh? But I think it's probably
one of the fluffiest
features he has.
You're wrong!
His tail isn't fluffy at all!
[gasping]
[meows]
What's the matter?
You aren't hurt
anywhere, are you?
Eureka!
[HAKASE]
Hold on a second!
Hakase?
[HAKASE]
Hey, Nano! Check it out!
I made a scarf that'll
let him talk!
[NANO]
What an amazing invention!
[HAKASE] Now, let's have
Sakamoto try it out.
Sakamoto?
You decided to call
the cat Sakamoto?
Yup! 'Cause it's the name
that's on his box.
I guess that's the simplest
way to go about it.
[HAKASE]
Okay! All done!
You think he's
really gonna talk?
He'll talk, all right.
[BOTH]
Here it comes.
[SAKAMOTO] I don't care
who you think you are,
that petting was excessive.
[HAKASE, NANO]
Huh?
[SAKAMOTO]
Also, it's common knowledge
that a cat meows
when it's hungry.
Not that it matters, since I
can spell it out for you now.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't aware of that.
[SAKAMOTO]
And then there's you!
Taking the name straight
from the side of the box?
Have some imagination.
[gasps] I'm so sorry.
I told you the same thing,
so I agree with him.
[HAKASE]
Yeah, but!
[SAKAMOTO]
How old are you two anyway?
[HAKASE]
Eight years old.
[NANO]
I'm one year old.
[SAKAMOTO] In your human years,
I'd be 20 years old.
It's Mr. Sakamoto. Capiche?
[BOTH]
Capiche...?
[SAKAMOTO] While I do appreciate
the free room and board,
there needs to be
some ground rules.
And you'll respect those rules
since I'm the oldest one here.
Another thing you should
know about cats...
Just because we're fluffy,
doesn't mean we can be
pet indiscriminately.
[NANO, HAKASE]
Umm...
[SAKAMOTO] To be honest
with you, I enjoy being pet.
But there's a limit.
You understand?
Life is all about moderation.
[NANO] I'll go put him back
where you found him.
[HAKASE]
'Kay...
[SAKAMOTO gasping]
[HAKASE]
Huh?
[SAKAMOTO]
My humblest apologies.
[PRINCIPAL]
Hm?
[PRINCIPAL gasping]
[laughing]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
[LANDLADY A]
Here you are!
Really?
But I'm late on my rent
payment again this month.
And you're still okay with
giving me free food?
It's fine, I'll always here
to help someone in need.
If there's anything else I can
do, feel free to let me know.
Do you mean it?
Well then, uh...
How about some money?
For the rent.
Don't think that I'm going
to let a greedy goblin
take advantage of my kindness.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Now. Vice-Principal.
Is this...?
What, is something
the matter, Principal?
You're sweating.
Why don't you go ahead and
look inside the doll's body?
[PRINCIPAL whimpers]
[pants, yells]
[bell rings]
[YUUKO] If I win this thing, I
don't owe you the extra snacks
from any of our previous deals.
Got it?
Yeah.
[YUUKO]
I'm totally gonna win!
[MIO] The battle for snacks
and juice begins!
Ready... Go!
[YUUKO laughing]
It's okay, Mai!
You were a little
early on the start.
Isn't that right, Mio?
I suppose it's possible she
jumped the gun. Just a tad.
See? It's fine.
We can start over!
Arm wrestlers,
take your positions.
Ready... Go!
[YUUKO grunting]
And Mai is the winner!
[YUUKO laughs]
Huh?
You caught me off guard!
I'll admit, I might have
underestimated you.
But now I'm all warmed up
and ready to go for real.
All right, bring it on!
[YUUKO] Man, I didn't think my
arm would still be this sore!
It's from my all-nighter!
But I'm just gonna shake it off
and get my head in the game.
'Bout time I got serious.
Think you can handle me?
[YUUKO] Ah, dang it!
I completely spaced on that one!
I can't believe I threw
three rounds in a row!
I never woulda seen that coming!
That's quite the surprise!
Okay. That's enough.
Hold on. Just you wait and see.
Mm-hm, I get it. I understand
what happened now.
Of course! It's simple!
You're all out of
beginner's luck,
and now it's the end for you!
Prepare to meet your doom!
Ready!
[YUUKO] Well, isn't this an
interesting turn of events?
What do they call you again?
--[MIO] Hey now.
--The immoveable object, right?
Mio, hold this for me!
'Cause I'm about to unleash
the unstoppable force.
Prepare for something
really special!
Would you please cut that out?!
It's because you're
not even trying!
I can't fight for real if you
don't take this seriously!
Come at me with everything
you've got this time!
I'll unleash my ultimate moves!
Earth Destroyer!
Shooting Star!
Death! [groans]
Death!
[banging]
[YUUKO]
Why? I don't get it.
Why does it have to be this way?
It's only arm wrestling.
How can you be so
freakin' good at it?
I completely forgot I had
to pee this entire time.
I'll be right back.
I knew something was throwing me
off from the very beginning.
[MAI]
Yuuko?
One extra snack
from the station.
And 23 juices.
My stupid arm cramp got
me caught and yelled at
for not doing my homework.
Today really is the worst.
More importantly, tell me!
I need to know what
happens to Masao!
Come on, Mai!
Okay fine, I'll buy
you another juice
if you show me what
happens next.
--[MAI] Here.
--[YUUKO] Yoink.
[MASAO gasping]
[tiger roars]
[MASAO cheers]
[YUUKO]
I don't know what I expected.
[STRAW DOLL] What was that natto
doing inside of me anyway?
Was that supposed to
be some kind of joke?
Well, if it was,
it was "natto" very funny!
Really, that's
the last "straw."
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 4.
Look forward to it!