[YUUKO]
Hey, so, idea.
[MIO]
Yeah?
[YUUKO] We should throw Nano
a surprise birthday party!
[MIO] Oh, sure!
When do you wanna do it?
Today.
Today?
You could give us
more of a heads up
before planning this stuff.
My b!
'Kay. [groans]
I got nothin'.
What can we put
together in a day?
Well, I honestly don't even know
if today is her actual birthday,
so I wouldn't sweat
the details too much.
[MIO]
Then what's the point?
Because.
Because what?
That's what makes it a surprise!
I guess so?
[MAI]
Hakase, too.
[BOTH]
Huh?
We should also celebrate
Hakase's birthday today.
Ooh! Yeah, sure!
Knocking out two birthdays
at once? I like it!
[MIO]
Now that I think about it,
I guess surprise parties can
still be fun for everyone,
even if it's not
anybody's birthday.
[MIO]
Okay, I got it!
We should all go pick up a cake
for the party
after school today!
Let's do it!
Does that sound
good to you, Mai?
I left my purse at home.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh. That's all right.
Yuuko and I can split it then.
I actually forgot
my wallet, too.
[MIO gasps]
Please, Mio! We're beggin' ya!
Uh...
I suppose I never paid you back
for all that money I lost
at the amusement park.
So, don't worry about
the birthday cake.
It's on me.
[MAI, YUUKO gasp]
I'm gonna go tell Nano about
the awesome party we're
throwing for her!
It's supposed to be a surprise!
[gasps, chuckles]
Close one.
I forget how dumb you can be.
[gasps] Uh... Yeah?
Well, at least Koujirou
didn't shoot me down.
Wow!
Hey! I wasn't shot down!
Oh, yeah? Then why'd
you run away crying?
[MIO gasps]
I, uh...
I was just surprised by
the sudden turn of events
and needed a hot second
to process it all, 'kay?
Koujirou having a girl on his
arm doesn't mean anything!
And I haven't even tried
to tell him how I feel yet.
Unless he turns me
down to my face,
I won't give up on him!
He's the guy that
I love! Got it?
[YUUKO gasps]
[MIO whimpers]
--[YUUKO gasping]
--[MIO whimpering]
[MIO grunts]
So, deal with it! Okay?!
[NANO]
All right!
Do I have everything? Yup!
Hakase! I'm heading
off to school now!
[HAKASE]
Nano!
Yoink!
Huh?
[gasps]
[gasps] What'd you
do that for, Hakase?
Because! I made you a little guy
so I'm taking the big one off!
[squeals, gasps]
Hang on. What exactly do
you mean by "little guy"?
[HAKASE]
Here, I can show you.
It's, uh.
Are you saying that my
back could be smooth
with this "little guy"?
Uh--yeah, I guess.
[NANO gasps]
But this little guy can
do more than just that!
It can, uh... Wait, uh...
--Nano?
--Yes?
I kinda lost it.
[groans]
Oh, no!
What's the matter?
[SAKAMOTO]
Why are you being so rowdy
this early in the morning?
[SAKAMOTO gasps, screams]
[SAKAMOTO]
You little brat!
Stop leaving these weird
traps all over the place!
[gasps] Sakamoto broke the
little guy I was gonna give you!
Wha?
[SAKAMOTO]
Wait! Hang on, I, uh...
No. It was an accident!
Look! Mean old
Sakamoto made Nano cry!
[SAKAMOTO]
What are you talking about?
You're the one who left it on
the ground! It's not my fault!
[NANO sighs]
I'm gonna go to school now.
[HAKASE gasping]
[HAKASE]
Nano! You forgot this!
[NANO sighs]
I, uh...
I can make another one
if you want me to.
Would you be able to
finish it before I get home?
It's not hard for me
to make, so yeah.
[squeals] Okay!
I'll be back real soon!
Great!
--[SAKAMOTO sighs]
--[NANO] All right, I'm off!
[HAKASE]
See ya later!
[SAKAMOTO]
Yeah. See ya.
[panting]
[OURA]
Oh, my, how bizarre.
[PRINCIPAL]
Huh?
Vice-Principal!
[OURA] If it isn't the statue of
me that stood in this very place
when I held the position of
principal at this school.
Yes. Strange indeed.
I wonder what happened to your
statue, Principal Shinonome.
[PRINCIPAL panting]
[OURA chuckles] These young
students do the darndest things.
I simply can't understand the
humor behind pranks like these.
It just doesn't make any sense!
Unless there is a reason.
[gasps]
Perhaps I have some secret
supporters in the student body.
[OURA chuckles]
[panting]
[DELIVERY MAN 26A]
Vice-Principal!
We finished your delivery!
[gasps]
This is where you wanted us
to put the statue, right, sir?
[OURA] Uh, well, um,
you must be mistaken.
[BOTH panting]
Hey wait. Was this...
your doing?
Uh--that's ridiculous.
This must be another part of the
prank the students are pulling.
It's quite elaborate,
don't you think?
Excuse me, young man,
but could you take this
statue away as well?
Huh? You really want us to
take this dinky statue back?
[OURA]
Dinky?!
Understood, sir!
We'll be hauling this ugly thing
out of your sight immediately!
[OURA]
Ugly?!
Hey! We gotta load up this
pathetic-looking one, too!
[gasps]
It's okay, Vice-Principal.
Don't take it personally.
We can put it right
next to the crappy one
we already have on
the back of the truck!
[PRINCIPAL]
What?!
[DAIKU]
Huh? It's unlocked.
Hmm?
Oh, wow, I didn't expect
you to be so early.
I thought I'd be
the first one here.
I took the blackbird
and everything.
So, did you come in to take
part in the morning practice?
Well, I...
I, uh... just, uh...
I did!
[DAIKU]
What? Really?
Yes.
[SEKIGUCHI gasps]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MIO sighs] I should've
known that I would end up
buying both of
your lunches, too.
Sorry!
Nah, since you both
forgot your wallets,
I really don't mind it.
Wow! That's so generous of ya!
You're the bestest!
[MIO groans, coughs]
Whoa. I hit too hard.
Yeah. You should really
be more careful, you know.
That's my bad!
[MAI gasps]
That's my head.
Sorry, I didn't see
you there, Mai!
Me neither.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh! By the way, did you
end up asking Nano
if we could come over
to her place later today?
Crap! I totally forgot to!
[sighs]
So, I'll run and tell Nano about
her surprise party right away!
No! It's supposed
to be a surprise!
Just ask if we can hang
out at her house later!
I knew that, silly!
I don't think that you do!
Fine! I'll ask her myself!
--[MIO whining]
--Come on! I said I'd do it!
Yeah, and that's the problem!
[YUUKO]
Aww, you can trust me!
[MIO]
I really can't!
[MIO, YUUKO grunt]
I can ask her.
Uh--wait! Hang on, Mai!
Don't worry about it!
Just gimme a chance!
[YUUKO grunts, sighs]
'Kay, I'm gonna go find Nano
and ask about the thing!
I totally got this, guys!
[YUUKO panting]
[BOTH grunt]
[YUUKO gasps]
I'm sorry!
No worries.
Godspeed!
[YUUKO]
Uh, yeah, sure, thanks.
And I'm really sorry!
And, uh, bye!
Aw, man!
[gasps] But I
didn't want coffee.
[YUUKO]
Oh! That was my bad!
No big deal.
I get you're probably
in a hurry right now.
[YUUKO]
I am! But I'm still sorry!
Come on!
[gasps]
Uh?
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[YUUKO panting]
[gasps] Um! Excuse me!
No running in the hallway!
[sneezes]
[gasps]
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
Rainbow.
[YUUKO panting]
I just can't believe
that it's actually over!
[pants, screams]
[coos]
[gasps] Found it!
--[wings flapping]
--Huh? Huh...
[DOVE 13A cooing]
[PRINCIPAL chuckles]
[panting]
Aw man, that one stung.
--[NANO] Yuuko!
--Huh?
You're not hurt, are you?
Oh! You're just the
person I was looking for!
[NANO]
You were trying to find me?
Yeah! I actually wanted to--
[BOTH gasp]
Wait! That's not--!
I, uh...
[YUUKO]
Whoa! Are you okay?
I didn't hurt you, did I?
[NANO]
Oh. Don't worry. I'm all right.
Really? Well, that's good.
[gasps] And, uh, this isn't
what you think it is, I swear!
It's a trick I can do!
[YUUKO]
Anyway! I wanted to ask you
if me and the others could come
over to your place later today.
Huh? Sure you can.
Oh! Also, it's--!
Heh, heh, heh. I can't
tell you anything else,
'cause it's a surprise!
[NANO]
Um, okay.
[YUUKO]
We'll see you later then!
Yeah. Sure.
It looks like I'll
have to buy more
if Yuuko and the others
are stopping by.
Can you believe we
made it to the end?
[panting]
[ALL] ♪ First comes a rock,
what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors
and one, two, three! ♪
[gasps]
[HAKASE, SAKAMOTO]
What the heck?
[panting]
[YUUKO panting]
[YUUKO sighs]
[YUUKO yells]
[panting]
[YUUKO pants, grunts]
[PANTHER 26A roars]
[BOTH panting]
This dumb pumpkin is too strong!
[SAKAMOTO sighs]
I'm so sick of that kid.
Why does she always pull that--
[NAKAMURA]
Taisho?
Is that you, Taisho?
[gasps] It is!
[SAKAMOTO]
Wait! Nakamura?
I've been looking
all over for you!
I'm glad you're okay. [gasps]
Why are you running?
Don't you remember who I am?
[SAKAMOTO]
Of course I remember!
That's why I'm running!
[NAKAMURA]
Taisho, time for dinner.
Here.
[SAKAMOTO meows]
[NAKAMURA]
Hm? What's the matter, boy?
Are you not hungry? Huh? Huh.
[SAKAMOTO screeches]
[NAKAMURA gasps]
What's wrong, Taisho?
Time for your bath.
[SAKAMOTO meows]
And now.
[SAKAMOTO screeches]
Bad kitty!
Oh, no. I have to
hurry or I'll be late.
Okay, Taisho. I'll see
you when I get home.
Bye.
Wow! Close one. [sighs]
Gotta run.
[SAKAMOTO meows]
[SAKAMOTO panting]
Taisho!
Where'd you run off to, kitty?
[SAKAMOTO]
Just get out of here already!
[NANO]
Oh! Ms. Nakamura!
[SAKAMOTO gasps]
Nice to see you!
[NAKAMURA]
Uh, Nano?
[SAKAMOTO] Perfect!
I'm sure she can do something!
Is something the matter?
You looked like you
were searching...
[NAKAMURA]
It's like she's a robot moth
drawn to my flames of science!
But... I can locate
Miss Shinonome
any time I want at school.
Right now, my cat
takes priority.
Sorry to bother you,
but have you seen a
black cat around here?
Oh! You wouldn't happen to
own a black cat, would you?
What a fun coincidence!
Well. Sort of.
He ran away a while ago.
[NANO]
I'm sorry.
I have a black cat, too,
so I can sympathize.
That so?
[NANO] Would it be okay if
I helped you look for him?
Of course.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
[NANO]
Not at all!
[SAKAMOTO]
You are useless!
So, can you tell me
more about your cat?
I heard you call out
a name earlier.
What was it again?
It's Taisho.
That's an interesting
name for a cat.
Huh?
My cat's named Sakamoto,
because that's what was written
on the box we found him in!
That's a weird way
to name a cat.
That's true. It really is kind
of weird, I guess. [giggles]
Tell me, is he cute?
Huh?
Your cat Taisho?
Is he a cute kitty?
Heh. What a ridiculous question!
Of course he is.
[SAKAMOTO]
Well, it's not like she meant to
treat me poorly on purpose.
Then again, if she kept that up,
my day's probably
would've been numbered.
Wait, now that I think about it,
that's not any different
from how I have it right now!
If I were to compare the two,
they're equally bad!
[NANO]
Oh, it's this late already?
I'm sorry about
this, Ms. Nakamura,
but I have to start heading home
since this won't stay
fresh for very long.
Ah. Sure. That's fine.
When you find Taisho,
would it be okay if
I came to visit him?
[gasps] Of course!
You can visit whenever!
Any day! Tomorrow even!
Well, I look forward to it.
[NAKAMURA]
Same here!
[NAKAMURA chuckling]
[SAKAMOTO whines]
This--this sucks!
It doesn't matter who I go
with, they're both the worst!
[NANO]
Hakase! Sakamoto! I'm home!
[HAKASE]
Nano!
Here's the little guy!
[NANO gasps]
You really managed to finish it?
Yeah! But Sakamoto
stepped on it again!
[groans]
[NANO]
Sakamoto...
[HAKASE]
Yoink!
Wait. Did you--?
You're still okay
with taking that off?
I'll make another one, quick!
You're the best!
[HAKASE] ♪ This goes here,
and that goes here... ♪
I had no idea that this key
would come off so easily.
It wouldn't budge at all
whenever I attempted
to remove it by myself.
That was me!
I made it so you couldn't
take it off yourself,
but any other other person
could do it easy-peasy!
[NANO]
Of course she did.
Plot twist!
Anybody can hook it back up,
including you, Nano!
[NANO] That's an oddly
specific feature.
[NANO gasps]
I've been meaning to ask.
How will this new little guy
affect all the features I have?
--[HAKASE gasps]
--Huh?
Once you have this new part in,
your big toe won't be
able to fly off anymore.
[NANO]
I wouldn't consider it a loss.
[doorbell rings]
That must be Yuuko
and the others.
Wha? Yuuko! [giggles]
Yuuko's here!
Oh, that's right!
I should probably hide this key.
[NANO] I'm so glad I look
like normal person now.
Maybe I'll get along
better with everyone
without having to worry so much.
I'll be able to
do things normally.
I can just live my ordinary
life, doing ordinary things.
[YUUKO]
Anyway!
I wanted to ask you if
me and the others could
come over to your
place later today.
I wanna leave it on
'cause it looks cute.
[YUUKO] As long as you're
happy with who you are,
that's all that matters.
I just wanted to stop by
here and tell you that.
But I got distracted.
Nano!
[SAKAMOTO]
Hey, kid.
[YUUKO]
Shh! This is the important part!
Let's do it like we practiced!
[MIO]
All right, I got it.
[YUUKO, MIO]
Ready, and...
Hey, Nano!
Ta-da!
We brought a yummy cake for you!
To celebrate your birthday!
[NANO]
Huh? You all did what?
For my birthday?
Wait, how did you even--?
[YUUKO chuckles]
It was part of the surprise.
Are you surprised?
[HAKASE]
Is that cake? I want cake!
Gimme! I want cake!
I want it, I want it!
Hang on, Hakase!
You gotta wait your turn!
Be careful with that!
--[YUUKO laughing]
--We're all gonna share.
[ALL gasp]
Well, that sucks.
My cake!
[YUUKO]
What are we gonna do?
Mio spent a lotta money on that!
I brought another one.
[MIO, YUUKO]
Mai!
What the heck?
A shark!
[YUUKO, MIO laughing]
[HAKASE]
What was that? Do it again!
[YUUKO]
Nah! This time it's Mio's turn!
I wonder how they found out
today was my birthday.
I didn't tell anyone.
[HAKASE]
Nano!
I finished making
the little guy!
[NANO gasps]
Thanks, Hakase!
[HAKASE giggles]
Honestly, I always felt that
this key was inconvenient,
and I really wanted
to get rid of it.
But now,
I like it!
This key's part of
who I am! Huh?
Now, with this little guy in,
you have an extra feature
that makes your key
spin around and round
whenever you're genuinely happy
in your heart of hearts!
[NANO]
What's the point of that?
[HAKASE giggles]
[sighs]
Oh! That's right!
Hakase, do ya think
you could help me
carry this cake in
to the other room?
Whoa! You got another cake?
I'll be right behind you
after I make the tea.
Got it! Cake time, cake time,
cake time, cake time!
--[thud]
--[gasps]
Hakase? [gasps]
--[YUUKO, HAKASE] The cake.
--Not another one.
Hey! Be more careful
with stuff like that!
Are you okay?
Any way I can help?
[YUUKO] I just need something
to wipe this cake off me!
Right!
[MAI]
I'll put the candle on it.
--[MIO gasps]
--I wanna do it!
That's no fair!
We can save that for later.
Help us clean all
of this up first.
[NANO] We gotta clean it up
before the cake cakes!
[laughing]
[MIO]
Hang on, Mai!
Hang on. What' so funny?
I, um... Uh...
[MAI]
Another one.
[MIO]
No! Stop! One's enough!
[ALL chattering]
[NANO] I still don't
get what's happening!
--[NANO laughing]
--[ALL chattering]
[MAI]
I did it.
[MAI chuckles]
[MIO sneezes]
[MIO groans]
You better not have hay fever.
I'm fine, I just
can't stop sneezing.
Don't be silly!
If you wanna stop, you just
gotta have the motivation!
I don't understand
how motivation
has anything to do with
constant involuntary sneezing.
[YUUKO]
Hmm...
Sometimes, you just gotta do it!
No way.
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
What a complete idiot.