[giggles]
[NANO squeals]
[NANO] It's more beautiful than
I ever could've imagined!
[SAKAMOTO]
Hey, what's goin' on in here?
Just the best thing ever!
Hey, be careful over
there, Sakamoto!
[NANO] I wouldn't want
you getting your hair
on my nice new uniform.
You've been shedding
a lot lately.
[SAKAMOTO] I see how it is.
I'm just in the way now.
I'm changing, so wait out
here for a few seconds.
[giggles]
[gasps]
Check me out! Isn't this
the most perfect fit ever?
[SAKAMOTO]
Uh, well, yeah!
It was made based on
your measurements,
so of course it fits!
How do I look?
[SAKAMOTO]
You look pretty good, I guess.
[NANO] Ugh. You don't get it!
That's not what I meant at all!
Uh. Does it make me,
um... look normal?
[SAKAMOTO]
Sure.
I suppose you look like
any other school girl.
Do you really mean it?
You're the bestest kitty in
the whole world, Sakamoto!
Oh, wait! Fur!
[SAKAMOTO]
What is up with you today?
[NANO]
I'll tell you what's up. School!
And maybe even some new
friends on the horizon!
[SAKAMOTO]
I don't get it, but okay.
Oh, hey, Nano.
Wanna do what friends do
and grab some ice
cream after school?
Uh. Yeah. That sounds wonderful.
Great! How about we
go sing karaoke, too?
Huh? Really?
Well, um. Maybe.
I've never done that before!
Don't worry! I'll show you how!
Come on, everyone's going!
Oh. In that case, okay.
Wouldn't that be amazing?
Hi, Nano. Morning.
[NANO]
Oh, Hakase! Good morning!
Look at how well
the uniform fits me!
So, what do you think?
Do I look all right?
[HAKASE]
Um, yeah! You look cool!
[gasps]
Thanks, Hakase!
And I think you look
cool in your pajamas!
[HAKASE]
You mean it? I'm cool?
You are super-duper cool!
[SAKAMOTO] But she wears that
same thing all the time.
[HAKASE] Sakamoto! Don't
worry, you're cool, too!
[NANO] Handkerchief, check!
Student ID, check!
Textbooks, check!
Notebook, check!
Pencils, check!
Extra lead, check!
And mechanical pencil, check!
Okay! Everything is here!
[HAKASE snickers]
What is it?
You're forgetting something.
Huh? Am I really?
What'll you do if you're hungry?
Grab a Snickers!
Good thinkin'!
I left some food in
the kitchen for you.
There should be enough
for breakfast and lunch.
And I'll take care of the
laundry later today,
so make sure to gather the
clothes you want washed
before I get home from school.
Okay, but what time will you
be getting out of school?
Well, it ends around
3:30, I think.
But I'll need to do some
shopping for dinner
on the way back,
so I should be home by
5:00, at the latest.
At 5:00?
What's up? Did I forget
to tell you that?
[HAKASE]
Five o'clock is like nighttime.
I guess. But that's just
how it's gotta be.
'Kay, I'll be on my wa--
Hey, uh, what's the problem?
I changed my mind!
What?
But you were completely on
board with it a second ago.
I don't want you
to go! You can't go!
No way! I'm gonna be
late for school!
So could you please just
give me back my--
Ah! My left hand!
[HAKASE] Rolly, rolly, rolly,
rolly, rolly, rolly, roll.
[SAKAMOTO] Listen, kid! Now
really isn't the time for this.
Hakase.
How about I make it
up to you by cooking
your favorite rice
omelet for dinner?
No strings attached!
Okay then.
I'll pick up some
shark castellas
while I'm out shopping.
And I'll, uh... I'll throw in
an extra strawberry juice, too!
[HAKASE] Rolly, rolly, rolly,
rolly, rolly, rolly, roll.
Also.
What is it?
Win the Akutagawa prize.
[NANO]
But that's impossible!
[NANO] I was starting to get
worried there for a second,
but thankfully, I was
able to convince her.
Today marks the first
step towards me
becoming a normal person!
[NANO] Oh, no! It totally
slipped my mind!
What am I gonna do about
this key on my back?
[MIO, YUUKO] Things we
think are freakin' cool!
[STUDENT A chuckles]
Let's do this! It's time
to get to work!
[MIO, YUUKO] Awesome!
A motivated upperclassman!
[NANO]
What should I do?
I've been thinking all morning,
but I can't come up
with anything.
And there's no way
I can back out now.
[IZUMI]
Now then, I'd like to introduce
our new transfer student.
Miss Shinonome?
[NANO]
Yes!
[NANO] I knew it! Everyone's
freaked out by my key!
[IZUMI]
Here.
Miss Shinonome, take this
and write your name
on the chalkboard, please.
[NANO] Oh, no. Now they're
all staring at my back!
I've gotta come up
with an excuse quick!
[NANO] Uh, hi.
My name's Nano Shinonome!
And, um, you see.
I, uh, I was on my way to
school, and then I fell?
And a key got stuck to me!
[NANO] That made it worse!
How do I fix this?
Uh, that story I told you,
just, uh, forget about it!
I was kidding!
[NANO] Oh, no! Now it's
even more suspicious!
Uh, let's see. I've gotta
say something. Anything!
It's not like my
big toe will fly off
and turn into a USB drive
if you wind up the key,
or anything weird
and robotic like that!
[NANO]
I'm so dead!
[YUUKO] ♪ Tomorrow the
weather will be nice! ♪
[YUUKO screams]
[DAIKU]
Come on, Sekiguchi.
Put the book down
and let's play something.
Please, I even brought
the Game of Life
for the two of us to play.
Man, this is so boring.
I guess we could try playing Go
for once, or maybe even soccer.
We are the Go+Soccer club.
[MAKOTO]
Um, excuse me!
Hello!
Is there where I can find
the Go+Soccer club?
[DAIKU]
Yeah?
Are you accepting new
members right now?
[SEKIGUCHI, DAIKU gasps]
[MAKOTO chuckles]
Welcome to the club!
So what do I call ya, kid?
I'm Makoto Sakurai,
and I'm a first year.
Well, my name's
Kenzaburou Daiku,
a second year and
the club president.
And this here's Sekiguchi,
who's also a first year.
[MAKOTO chuckles]
[DAIKU]
Come on in and have a seat!
[MAKOTO]
Yeah, okay.
So, what do you wanna play?
How 'bout a round
of this board game.
Well, uh, I was hoping
that we could practice.
[DAIKU]
For?
Um, for Go+Soccer?
[chuckles]
Don't be silly. That's
a fake game I made up.
It's not like it's supposed
to be a real sport.
See, this club is pretty much
just about relaxing inside
and playing a few random
games every once in a while.
Kinda like a recreational
thing. Know what I mean?
Sure.
[DAIKU]
Hm?
The thing is,
I was actually in a Go+Soccer
club in middle school.
[DAIKU]
Uh?
And I had absolutely
no idea there would be
a Go+Soccer club in
high school, too.
But then I saw those banners
hanging on front
of the building.
So I had to find
the club and join!
And not to brag, but I was the
MVP of my middle school club!
[DAIKU yells]
Uh, Miss Shinonome?
Oh. Yes?
Oh, I just... I was just
curious about something.
Uh, that thing on your back.
Uh! It's.... Uh, well.
Huh? Right. Yeah, no. Uh.
--[NANO] Um. This is-- Uh!
--[IZUMI] Well, I mean. Um!
[SEKIGUCHI] So then, if
Go+Soccer is a real sport,
how do you play?
Well, it can be
kinda complicated,
so it'd be better if I show you.
Here. I'll give you a
little demonstration.
First off is the lifting.
[MAKOTO]
After lifting, its Go stones!
And then you go into...
...a solo suplex!
[BOTH grunt]
And that's the
avalanche joseki !
Three Star Point!
[DAIKU]
That was incredible.
I never thought this club would
go anywhere when I started it.
But now, it's way cooler
than I ever imagined!
[barking]
[KIYOSHI]
Hey, wait up!
Where the heck do you think
you're running off to?
Buddy! Come back!
[yelps]
Sakamoto! C'mere!
C'mere! C'mere!
[SAKAMOTO] Hey! Are you
crazy?! Cut that out!
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR] If asked
what it is, it is spinning.
That's what I told him.
Yeah, you see what I mean, bro?
Hey, let's go!
[sighs]
I told you we'd
make it back early.
[NANO] I can't believe I messed
everything up on my first day.
Everyone probably
thinks I'm crazy.
[MIO] Oh, hey, Nano, did you
bring your own lunch?
Uh, yeah, I did.
It looks really tasty.
So, do you pack one every day?
Yes, I do!
Like a normal girl.
[NANO]
Hm?
You can look at this.
Wow. It is pretty cool.
Thank you!
Oh, hells yeah.
I'm right on time.
[MIO]
Uh, no. You're crazy late.
Lunch break is
almost over already.
I'm sorry!
My shoes flew off while
I was on my way back,
and they got stolen
by a car and a dog,
so it was a real pain
to get 'em back.
[MIO]
Huh?
That sounds fake, but
also kinda interesting.
I totally wanna hear
the whole story later.
But right now, I'm just glad
you made it here all right.
Hang on. Where's your lunch?
[YUUKO]
Hm?
I ate it while I was
on the way back.
[MIO]
Huh? What'd you have?
A twice-cooked pork lunch box.
[MIO]
Whoa! How did you even--?
Ugh. Never mind.
Anyway, did you wanna eat lunch
with the three of us, Nano?
[NANO gasps]
I'd really like to hang out with
you and get to know you better.
Um, okay.
[NANO]
Maybe I didn't freak them out
and they think I'm
normal after all.
Maybe I can even
make some friends!
Oh, hey, what's with that
strange key thing on your back?
Uh! Uhh...
It's definitely
nothing suspicious
if that's what you're
asking! So, uh...
You aren't actually like
some weird robot girl
or something, are ya?
[screams]
Don't be ridiculous, Yuuko.
Sorry, she can be kinda dense.
Oh, we're almost out of time.
Sorry, Nano. Let's have
lunch together tomorrow.
Let's see.
[KATASHINA] There's no way
they're gonna believe that!
[MIO]
Uh...
[NAKANOJOU]
No, seriously.
I climbed the entire mountain
looking for her, and by the...
Hey, Yuuko, what did you get me?
[YUUKO]
Hm? I got the yakisaba .
...but she's just
an urban legend.
Could you repeat that
one more time, please?
Uh. Yakisaba , right?
I said yakisoba !
[gasps]
Oh. Well...
I guess I heard you wrong and
got you a different thing.
Yeah, that's my bad.
Don't act like it's
not a big deal!
I asked for noodles and
you gave me a fried fish!
But can you blame me?
Those two names
sound so similar.
That's not the--
Uh.
[groans]
Whatever. I give up.
Just give me my rice.
[YUUKO]
Hm?
What rice?
The rice that comes
with the fish!
Oh. Yeah, no,
it's just the fish.
How am I supposed to
eat this by itself?!
Huh? But you didn't
clarify when you asked
for the yakisaba
in the first place.
I asked for yakisoba !
Yaki ! Soba !
They're noodles!
'Kay. I get it now.
On the bright side,
you could post this whole
story on social media
and I bet it'll be hilarious.
I don't own a computer!
Aww. Well, it's not my fault
you're missing out on a
chance to score some likes.
All right, fine. I'll run out
again and get you your food.
I just need money.
Why should I be the one who
has to pay for your mistakes?
'Cause I don't have
any money left on me.
Uh?
Okay, fine. Just hurry up
and come back quick.
We hardly have any time left.
[YUUKO]
You can count on me!
[MIO]
That's all I have.
[YUUKO]
Wha--?
One peso is all I have!
I can't believe the only
money in my wallet
is this peso I kept
as a souvenir.
[YUUKO]
Huh?
[MIO] What can I do
with a single peso?
[YUUKO]
One peso?
I don't know!
You're the one who caused
this mess in the first place!
You should be the
one to pay for it!
[YUUKO]
I already spent all my money
when I bought my lunch,
so I don't have any more.
And what am I supposed
to do about my lunch?
Well, I guess...
you could eat...
...the mackerel.
Mackerel?! Ugh!
You're just a never-ending
cycle of pissing me off!
And I'm sick of letting you
copy my homework every day!
Why don't you just do it
by yourself for a change?!
You idiot!
I understand that you're upset,
but the fact that I'm an idiot
has absolutely nothing to do
with me getting your
lunch order wrong.
[MIO]
It has everything to do with it!
Yeah? I'd like to hear why!
Only an idiot would
mishear me like that!
Hmph.
Everyone's guilty of making
a few mistakes
sometimes, ya know!
But you just have to overreact!
It's not the end of the world!
[MIO] I didn't eat breakfast,
so I needed that lunch
to keep me from
starving all day!
I wouldn't expect an idiot
like you to understand!
I'm not an idiot!
[MIO] You just said you
were an idiot earlier!
Oh, and FYI, I'm never letting
you copy my homework ever again,
so good luck!
Yeah, that's fine! But
this is a two-way street!
If I can't copy your homework,
then you can't copy mine either!
Why would I wanna copy your
homework in the first place?
Your answers would be as
wrong as my lunch order!
Which you never apologized
for, by the way!
So get on your knees and
apologize right now!
Fine, if that's what
you really want,
I guess I should just
bend over then!
How's that?
This good enough for you,
Miss Perfect Hearing?
There's my apology!
Are you happy now?! Are ya?!
What?! You call that weird
pose you did a bow?
No! It wasn't a bow because
I was just stretching!
And I'm never gonna
bow to you! Fool!
Why can't you just admit
that you messed up?
[YUUKO]
Because you pissed me off!
Also, calling me an idiot
would make you a hypocrite.
Did you remember those
weird doodles you drew?
'Cause I do!
[MIO gasps]
[MIO]
Wait, the doodles were, uh...
You moron, those were just--
[YUUKO]
What were they?
Go ahead and tell me!
I'm an idiot, so I won't get it
unless you spell it out for me!
Go ahead!
You moron!
You're a complete
and utter moron!
[YUUKO]
Ugh! Who's the moron?!
Only a real moron would
draw these weird sketches
and leave them out in the open!
[MIO screams]
Come on, I want you
to taste defeat!
Eat it along with
this yakisaba !
I wanted yakisoba !
Would you apologize already?
Get down on your
knobby knees right now!
[YUUKO]
I apologized earlier!
Was that not good
enough for you?
Apologize like you mean it,
or you're just a waste of space!
[YUUKO]
All right, fine!
I'll show you the ultimate
bow to end all bows!
Behold its glory!
The one true bow!
[MIO] Hmph. I see the bow,
but I don't hear an apology!
What are you sorry for? Tell me!
Say that you're sorry
for messing up my order!
Say it!
Say that you're an idiot
that messes things up!
And you're just a
useless human being
that can't get anything right!
Come on! I'm waiting!
Do it already!
Are you not listening?
Apologize, you moron!
Worthless! Idiot! Moron!
[yells]
[NANO screams]
[growling]
[BOTH scream]
I'm sick and tired of you
constantly calling me a moron!
You don't even know me!
We've only been
friends for like, what,
six lousy months now?
I could say the same about you!
You don't understand
me or my drawings!
I do understand!
Your drawings are so good
that you might as well become
a professional manga artist!
Uh! What are you talking about?
Stop being stupid, stupid.
Huh?
Well, if I'm stupid, then
you're stupid, too, so suck it!
You just called yourself stupid.
[YUUKO]
I did not!
But you did!
But that stupid side of
you isn't all that bad.
What are you saying?
You've got the good side!
Uh. Hey, you stop it now,
with your positive energy.
Well, I think you're way too
talented at drawing art things!
Shut up! You run too fast!
Well, you're too smart!
[MIO]
Well, you're optimistic!
You're a great person!
[MIO]
You're a super fun person!
[NANO gasps]
[NANO]
Amazing!
[TAKASAKI]
Captain! I'm sorry. We tried!
[SENPAI A] Save your tears.
We always have next year.
[TAKASAKI]
I'll win it! I'll win for him!
Woohoo!
[TAKASAKI]
Those were the days.
[HAKASE]
Hey, Nano,
did you have fun on
your very first day?
[NANO]
I sure did.
So many things happened.
It was kinda like...
Oo, like what? Tell me about it!
I love having friends!
It's the greatest feeling
in the whole world!
[gasps]
That sounds amazing!
[SAKAMOTO] Come on. You're
both getting too excited.
Huh? One of these?
Hakase!
Please take this key
off of my back!
Uh...
No way.
[NANO]
Huh? But why not?
It's having a negative impact
on my life at school!
People are already
starting to suspect
that I might really be a robot!
And that makes it harder
for me to make friends.
[HAKASE] You can to make
friends. Your key is pretty.
[NANO]
I don't think it is.
[HAKASE]
But it's cute. And it's a key.
[NANO]
But why?
[SAKAMOTO] Just hurry up
and give me my food.
[SOCCER BALL A]
It's soccer ball here.
All I do is get kicked around,
day in and day out.
Kicked and crushed until I
deflate and get put to rest!
I don't even have goals!
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 15.
Look forward to it!