[bell chimes]
Okay, the testing
period is over.
[STUDENTS]
Yay!
[TAKASAKI] Whoa. That's
quite the celebration.
They must be relieved after
putting so much effort
into their studies.
It warms my heart.
[STUDENT D] ♪ The test is over!
And it was a snap! ♪
My life flashed
before my eyes.
Am I dreaming? Pinch me
as hard as you can!
We finished!
Nothing can hurt you now.
My parents are sending
each and every one
of you a bag of rice as a gift!
[STUDENT G]
Yeah! Thanks rice man!
[FESTUDENT F] The two of us
are getting married!
[STUDENTS]
Wow!
[STUDENT G]
Come on! All together now!
Hip-hip...
[STUDENTS]
Hooray!
[TAKASAKI]
What the--? Could you not?
--This is overkill!
--[STUDENTS] Hooray! Hooray!
[door clicks]
[door slams]
[yawns]
[YOSHINO]
Ah, Mio. Good morrow.
[YOSHINO gasps]
No, this is all wrong!
You're supposed to
say something like,
"Huh? Uh. The heck is that?"
Be surprised!
Aw, you're not still
mad at me, are you?
Can't you just admit
it was kinda funny?
I made your mont blanc a Knight.
Nah, I still could've eaten it
if I took that chess piece out,
so it really wasn't
that big of a deal.
[gasps]
[MIO grunts]
Yeah, right!
Sis! Why?!
How could you do that to me?!
I was so looking forward to
my dessert, and you knew it!
Why did you have to stick
a knight on the top?!
I guess... I thought
it'd look cool.
Head!
You'd think she'd be used to my
practical jokes at this point.
[MIO]
Gah, she's so annoying.
They only make ten of
those mont blancs a day.
[MIO]
Not that it matters.
Cause even if she knew that,
she's always pulling
stuff like this.
I thought now that
she's in college,
she'd finally understand
when to stop.
But whatever, it's fine.
I can let it slide for today,
because I've got
better things to do. And she
has absolutely no idea!
I knew she'd be up to
something, so I was ready.
I disguised my shortcake,
so it's safe and sound.
Ahh!
[MIO]
Checkmate! She got me!
I can't believe
she freakin' got me!
[MIO]
The strawberry!
She stole the crown
jewel of my rare,
only-five-made-per-day
gourmet shortcake!
Don't you worry, Strawberry!
I'm coming for you!
Hold on!
[MIO grunts]
Where is it?
What did you do to my precious,
delicious, sweet...?!
[YOSHINO]
Namaste.
--[MIO] Gut!
--[YOSHINO groans]
[MIO cries]
Why are you so mean to me?
A shortcake without
the strawberry
isn't special anymore!
[MIO] Now it's just a stupid,
normal piece of shortcake!
[MIO cries]
[YOSHINO] ♪ Happy birthday
to me, happy birthday to me ♪
♪ Happy birthday dear Yoshino ♪
♪ Happy birthday to me ♪
[MIO]
Sis...
[YOSHINO]
Mio.
--[thud]
--[YOSHINO groans]
[MIO]
Today isn't even your birthday!
[YUUKO humming]
I've been wanting to try
this place for forever!
And didn't you see it
in a magazine?
Sure did.
And it came with a coupon!
[MIO]
No point in showing it to me.
[MAI]
I'm having the Herring Soba.
Ah, hot dish in this weather?
You connoisseur.
[MAI]
With no herring.
[laughing] Then that's
just noodles in water!
Ah...
Ah-hem. And what're
you going to get, Mio?
[MIO] I think I'm gonna
get the Zaru Soba.
Ah, the classic pick for a
non-foodie That's a safe one.
[MIO] It's good enough for me.
What're you getting?
I think I'm gonna have myself
the Summer Veggie
Tempura Special.
It's pretty bold to go with a
rice dish at a noodle place.
Right?
[MIO]
Yeah, if you say so.
You get it! It's a
seasonal item, too.
This kind of dish is special,
so you never know
when it'll be back.
Probably next summer.
Maybe you don't get it.
Haven't you ever heard of
living in the moment, Mio?
What matters most
is the here and now!
[MIO]
Oh, really?
I'm sure you'll understand
what I mean one day.
[MIO]
Yeah, okay.
Excuse me!
[WAITRESS A]
What would you like to order?
One Herring Soba, a Zaru Soba,
and... the seasonal...
special dish...
[WAITRESS 9A] Herring Soba,
Zaru Soba, and a Summer Veggie
Tempura Special. I'll be
back with your order soon.
[MIO] I heard they make
all of their soba noodles
by hand at this place.
[YUUKO] Can't get any more
authentic than that!
Oh, I wonder what this buckwheat
dumpling thing is.
[MIO] It's the squishy stuff
they make using the soba flour!
[YUUKO]
Wow, for real?
[WAITRESS A]
Thank you for waiting.
[gasping]
[WAITRESS A]
This is the Herring Soba here,
and the order of the
Zaru Soba for you.
I don't mind if you guys start
eating your food without me!
If you're sure...
Before it gets cold.
But mine's supposed to be cold.
[YUUKO] It must be because my
order is from the seasonal menu.
I bet they're taking extra
time and care to make it!
[slurping]
Your food is taking a while.
Guess they need extra time
to fry all those vegetables.
Or maybe they went out to
pick 'em, so they're fresh!
[MIO, YUUKO laughing]
That's it! No wonder
they're slow!
I think you could order your
food a la carte here too.
[MIO]
Hm, really?
[footsteps]
[YUUKO gasping]
Finally!
[MIO]
Another table's.
[MAI]
Too bad.
[MIO slurping]
God Dammit!
[MIO]
Hey! Just settle down, Yuuko!
[YUUKO] How can I?!
This is taking freakin' forever!
I don't care if they're famous,
even if they capture
the flavors, they'll never
capture my feelings!
[MIO]
You're not making any sense!
[YUUKO]
They're gonna feel my wrath!
[WAITRESS A]
Thank you for waiting.
'Bout time! Do you
know how long I--
[WAITRESS A cries]
Uh, thanks.
You guys can like,
read a book or something.
This might take a little bit.
[BOTH] Things we think
are freakin' cool!
Uh.
[MEN gasping]
[MIO, YUUKO]
Young chess players!
[insects buzzing]
[YUUKO] I've got my
mosquito repellent going,
but I thought it'd be
doing more than it is.
They won't leave
in the late night.
Mogami River.
Ha!
[YUUKO grumbles]
Ha! Huh! H'ya!
[buzzing continues]
[inhales]
Well, it looks like you're just
minding your own
business anyway.
Guess I'll go crawl
back into bed then.
Sneak attack!
Victory!
Bug off!
I have taken a precious life.
[buzzing]
I'll do it again!
[YUUKO grunting]
[YUUKO]
I hit! And I smack!
But they never
learn their lesson!
But what else can I do?
I'm running out of options!
[YUUKO]
Listen, Mom!
We can't live in this
infested house anymore!
We just have to move! Now!
[groans]
Do you have any idea
what time it is?!
Now shut up and go to sleep!
[buzzing]
[buzzing continues]
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
Chirashizushi. You try.
[MALE OGRE 9A]
Tsurasuzusu.
No! Chi-ra-shi-zu-shi!
Go!
[MALE OGRE 9A]
Tsu-ra-su-zu-su.
No, no! Chi.
[MALE OGRE 9A]
Chi.
[ANGEL A]
Ra.
[MALE OGRE 9A]
[ANGEL A]
Shi.
[MALE OGRE 9A]
[ANGEL A]
Zu.
[MALE OGRE 9A]
[ANGEL A]
Shi.
[MALE OGRE 9A]
Yes! Chirashizushi. Go!
Tsurasuzusu.
[HAKASE]
Sakamoto! Check it out!
The bottom of this popsicle
says I'm a winner!
See, look at it!
[NANO] You really shouldn't
be eating that right now.
Why can't I eat it?!
Well because, it's gonna
spoil your appetite.
Yummy!
[SAKAMOTO] I don't get why
you got so worked up
over a popsicle stick.
You're such a child.
It wasn't a normal stick!
I won it upside-down!
[SAKAMOTO] Doesn't matter which
way the stick is going when
the outcome's the same. So,
you found out two bites earlier.
Big deal.
Seriously. You kids
can be so easy to please.
You get excited over
the smallest things.
[SAKAMOTO gasps]
It's a crab!
They never show up!
It's like one in a million!
I'm gonna save you
for last, little guy!
Thank you very
much for the meal.
What's this?
You've barely eaten
any your food, Hakase.
Let me guess, you had snacks
this afternoon, didn't you?
I'm not proud of it.
How many times have I told you
not to snack before meals?!
All gone.
[NANO]
All gone?!
You ate a whole month's
worth of snacks?!
That wasn't a compliment!
What am I gonna do with you.
[HAKASE] I only did it because
Sakamoto told me to!
[NANO]
Is that true?!
[HAKASE]
Sakamoto said food gets yucky
faster in the summer
so I had to do it.
[SAKAMOTO] I didn't mean
you had to eat all of them.
[HAKASE] Snacks go in the tummy.
Where else would I put them?
[SAKAMOTO]
What kind of argument is that?
[NANO]
Sakamoto!
[SAKAMOTO] Why are you even
considering her side?
If you look at it objectively,
the situation's pretty
black-and-white!
But you only have black fur.
[NANO]
That's true.
[SAKAMOTO] Uh, what does that
have to do with anything?
[NANO]
That's enough.
There's no point in
arguing anymore.
I've decided...
Hakase won't be getting
her strawberry juice.
[HAKASE gasping]
[HAKASE]
Uh. I won't eat anymore snacks!
[NANO]
I said no.
[HAKASE] I'll give you my
winning popsicle stick!
[NANO]
I don't want it!
[HAKASE]
I'll eat all of my vegetables!
[NANO]
You better!
Hmph.
[HAKASE cries] I'll take
the key off your back!
[NANO gasps]
[NANO]
I'll let it slide this one time.
But next time, no snacks
for a month. I mean it.
Okay!
So...
[HAKASE gasping]
[NANO]
Wait, if I give it to her now,
I feel like our deal
is gonna fall through.
You can have your juice after
you take the key off my back.
Ahh!
Fine then. Gimme a sec.
Huh? 'Kay!
Hakase!
[NANO screams]
Your right hand's a loser.
How did you even
come up with this?!
Not a compliment!
I'd appreciate it if you
stopped messing with me.
Could you please consider
my feelings for a change--
You're not listening!
[CHILDREN chattering]
[CHILDREN]
Rock, paper, scissors!
[GIRL 9A gasps, giggles]
[GIRL 9A gasps]
Mine!
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
If you look hard enough,
you can find anything.
[yawns]
[YOSHINO]
Oh, Mio! I'm glad you're here.
What do you want, Yoshino?
Something came up,
and I was wondering...
I said I'd help out the
neighborhood association.
Would you please take my place?
Huh? Why don't you ask
Mom instead of me?
[YOSHINO] Oh, she's busy
playing kick volleyball
with her friends. To say thanks,
I'll pay you 10,000 yen.
I'm counting on you!
[MIO]
I guess I could use the money.
Not like I'm doing
anything anyway.
Think I should try a Mohawk
fade with some dreads?
[WOMAN 9A] Check it out!
That's so cute!
[MIO gasps]
I've been bamboozled!
This whole thing sucks!
What am I even doing?!
How did this happen?
Why did I agree to this?
Come and get your delicious...
[MIO] The neighborhood
association's big plan
was to sell daifuku
on the street?
And with just two people?
[WOMAN 9C]
Nah, I'll pass.
[MIO]
It's embarrassing!
No wait...
It's too embarrassing!
Everyone's staring at
me like I'm an idiot!
How am I supposed
to draw people in
when I'm dressed like their
weird Daifuku-Dude mascot?
There aren't even
any facial features.
It's just a plain,
white ball for a head!
What even makes this
mascot a dude, anyway?
It's just a big daifuku !
[MIO gasps] Come to think
of it, this Daifuku Fair...
...doesn't seem fair to me!
[GIRL B laughing]
[GIRL B groans]
Uh. I'm sorry--
[GIRL 9B screams, cries]
[MOTHER 9A]
Sweetie! It's okay!
[MIO]
This is the absolute worst.
[MAA]
Whoa! What's that thing?
It looks gross!
[laughs] Take this,
gross thingy!
[MIO] Stop it, please!
That kinda hurts, so cut it out!
Seriously! I mean it! There's
no padding in this costume!
Okay, it's starting to
really hurt, so please!
Could you just...
Cut it out!
Ah! She's mad! Run for it!
[OSAMU]
Yeah! Let's get outta here!
[MAA]
What a freaky freak!
[MIO sighs]
Could this get any worse?
[YUUKO laughs]
[MIO]
Huh?
[screaming]
[laughing]
[MIO]
Yuuko!
--[YUUKO laughing]
--[MIO grunting]
[MIO sighs]
Stop tarnishing the
Daifuku reputation.
[MIO gasping]
I can't watch. Hand it over.
I'll show you!
Useless part-timers!
Don't just stand there.
Go and work behind the counter.
'Kay?
[MIO]
Yeah...
[MIO] I swear. This 10,000
yen better be worth it.
[NAKANOJOU'S FATHER chuckles]
[NAKANOJOU'S FATHER]
♪ Tokachi! Azuki beans! ♪
--♪ Wasanbon sugar! ♪
--[MIO] Can I leave?
[MIO sighs]
I just wanna go home.
Well, I guess these daifuku
look pretty nice,
but are they even gonna sell?
[MAN 9G]
Excuse me.
How much for one of these?
[MIO]
A customer!
It's, uh...
[MIO]
I have no idea.
Uh, sir! How much
does one daifuku --
[NAKANOJOU'S FATHER]
Maybe this was a bad idea.
[gasps]
[NAKANOJOU'S FATHER]
I couldn't run even if I tried!
I'm strawberry filled!
[MIO]
Uh, yeah.
You could just take it for free.
[MAN 9G]
Cool! Lucky me!
[insect buzzing]
--[buzzing]
--[NANO groans]
Ha!
[NANO groans]
[SHINONOME NARRATOR]
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome household.
[KING]
Greetings! I'm the King!
Check me out! Looks like
I'm pretty isolated.
I better find my
chess mates soon!
The set is missing
a major piece!
Hope it doesn't get pawned off!
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 10!
Look forward to it!