[bell chimes]
[PRINCIPAL] I've noticed
some unruly behavior
among the students as of late.
And since you are the
school's guidance counselor,
I trust that you'll be
stricter with students
and enforce our rules.
[IZUMI]
Of course!
Yes! You can count on me!
[STUDENT C]
Just trust me, the next time...
[IZUMI]
That's right!
Becoming the guidance counselor
was the first step I took
to growing as a person!
I have to do my best!
[gasps]
[IZUMI yelps]
[IZUMI] Oh, my goodness!
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
Wait, just calm down.
You can do this.
[IZUMI]
Um. Excuse me!
Uh. What can I
do for you, madam?
I'm sorry to bother you, but
you see, uh, I was thinking
that it might be inappropriate
to eat while walking?
Or something like that.
[laughs] Apologies!
I skipped breakfast
this morning.
And my stomach couldn't
wait until lunchtime.
But I shall put this
away immediately.
You mean it? Thank you so much!
I'm really glad you understand.
[IZUMI] That wasn't so bad.
All I had to do was speak up.
[KOUJIROU]
Please tell the chef...
[gasps]
...the meal was to die for!
[IZUMI gasping]
If you don't stop making
a scene in the hallway,
you really will die here,
so quit being such
a weirdo at school!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I don't think
those are allowed?
[WEBOSHII]
Hey, Misato! We're headed out!
Coming!
Sasahara! We'll continue this
during the lunch break.
Don't you forget it!
[IZUMI] The principal was right
about the unruly behavior.
[KOUJIROU]
My apologies.
I'm sure she meant no harm.
She tends to be a bit dramatic.
Don't mind her.
Uh, okay. I guess,
if you say so.
Oh! One more thing!
Question.
What do you call that frilly
piece of cloth around your neck?
Ah, you mean this?
[IZUMI] Yes, I have to say,
it looks rather dashing.
We live our ordinary lives,
day after day, in succession.
Each hour can be considered
a miracle in itself.
[IZUMI]
Uh.
So, you see. Each moment
should be truly savored.
[gasps] So, uh, you
never actually said
what that frilly thing was.
[gasps]
[laughing]
Ahh! That's a good one!
[IZUMI gasping]
[KOUJIROU] Now, then.
I bid you adieu, madam.
[IZUMI stutters]
[IZUMI]
Thank you. I appreciate it.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[STUDENT D] ...Go+Soccer club is
a club that plays Go and Soccer.
Both individually,
and at the same time.
[IZUMI] Excuse me, Nakanojou!
A moment please?
Yes. How can I help you?
Uh, well, you see, thing is...
I was just thinking
that your haircut
might be a little too
extreme for school.
Uhh...
Uh. I mean,
just by a little bit!
On second thought,
it's not all that bad.
[NAKANOJOU]
It's all I have.
Hey, I'm really sorry
if I offended you.
I was only saying--
My hair.
My hair doesn't grow
out on the sides!
[IZUMI whimpers]
[DAIKU]
Green light!
Still green light.
Green light...
And red light!
[SEKIGUCHI]
Everyone went home already.
[HAKASE]
Um, what are these?
Those are green plums.
I thought it might
be kind of fun
if I tried pickling some
of them at home this year.
Pickled plums are so sour.
But they're very
healthy for you.
Plus, if you put them
inside of rice balls,
it'll keep the rice
from going bad.
Ah! Yum!
[gasping] Hey, Nano!
I think not.
Gah! You say no, but I haven't
even asked anything yet!
We bought you plenty of snacks
the other day, and I thought
I made it clear that we're
not going to buy any more
of them until you finish the
ones you already have at home.
Are you listening to me?
Remember we came
here for a purpose.
To shop for... uh...?
Sakamoto.
Right. We told Sakamoto
that this grocery trip
was to get him food, so we
can't get distracted by...
Whoa that's giant.
Um, 'Scuse me.
Yes? Anything I can
help you with?
That thing up there.
Is it new?
Yes, our snowman just
came in this morning.
It's the only one we
have in the whole store.
Can I eat it?
[NANO] Well, I guess it
wouldn't be too different
from a shaved ice dessert.
Oh, it's cold!
And cheap, too!
Gonna buy it?
Uh. No, I was just wondering
how much it was!
Check out the snow man.
I want it.
[NANO]
Uh.
[OLD LADY A]
Young lady.
Yes ma'am?
If you're not going to buy that
snowman, please give it to me.
Okay, I'll take it!
[HAKASE grumbles] So, I don't
get to buy anything,
but you can buy whatever you
want? You're such a big meany.
Listen. It's not like that.
Yes, it is! You wouldn't
let me get my favoritest snacks,
but you picked up a snowman
just cause he's cute.
It's not fair!
I wanna buy stuff too!
Okay, fine, I give--
you can get one snack.
Do you mean it?
All right. We're good.
[NANO laughs]
[SAKAMOTO] So that's why you
ended up buying that thing.
Uh-huh! It's cute, it's cold,
and I like how it feels.
[HAKASE humming]
[SAKAMOTO]
Hmm...
Okey-dokey, here's some more.
[HAKASE]
Yay!
Nano, I need more snow!
Right away!
[NANO]
Coming right up!
[SAKAMOTO]
You two are unbelievable.
Anyway, where's the
food you got for me?
[gasps]
[SAKAMOTO]
Oh.
She forgot my food.
That's snow way to treat a cat.
Talk about a cold shoulder.
[BOTH] ♪ First comes a rock,
what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors
and a one, two, three! ♪
[HAKASE]
Up and away...
The screw!
[MIO gasps]
[YUUKO whimpers]
[gasps]
[gasping]
Uhh...
[YUUKO groans]
[YUUKO gasping]
[screaming]
[YUUKO]
That's not it.
[MAI sighs]
[YUUKO screaming]
[PRINCIPAL muffled screaming]
[bell tolls]
Okay! It's time to
turn in your tests!
[YUUKO]
Say what?!
[YUUKO whimpers]
That was a bald cap.
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR]
Figuring out what people want
is no simple task.
Because all people want
different things in life.
Instead, focus on what
your own goals are.
That can be easier to grasp.
From there, do the best
you can and have faith.
That's all we can do.
We work hard, and hope life
takes us down the right path.
[DAIKU]
Still green light.
Green light...
And red light!
[SEKIGUCHI]
Are we still not done?
[inhales, groans]
I got sent out to
the hall again.
Huh?
I'm finally starting to
get used to this body.
[YUUKO screams]
[NANO gasping]
[NANO] Just looking at
them is making me hungry.
[HAKASE]
♪ Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair ♪
♪ Fuzzy Wuzzy... ♪
[SAKAMOTO]
What're these?
These are called pickled plums!
They're quite delicious!
[SAKAMOTO]
Oh.
Huh? Uh!
You can't eat them yet!
They won't be ready
for a little while!
[HAKASE laughs]
Hey, Sakamoto!
Come play with me!
[NANO]
Oh, a foxtail.
[HAKASE] Come on, pretty kitty.
Here, Sakamoto.
[SAKAMOTO] That's "Mister"
Sakamoto to you, ya little brat!
Or did you forget already?
Oh yeah, I did forget.
Sorry, Sakamoto.
[SAKAMOTO] Now you're
just doing it on purpose!
I just forgot again!
But I promise I'll remember
it next time, Sakamoto.
[SAKAMOTO hisses]
Do you mock me, child?
[NANO]
All right, I'm off to the store!
See ya later!
[SAKAMOTO] Jeez. You two really
need to learn some manners.
You've got no respect.
Sorry, Sakamoto.
I'm not doing it on purpose.
[SAKAMOTO] Could you,
for once, add the "mister"?
Want some gum?
Would that help, Sakamoto?
[SAKAMOTO] How many times
do I have to tell you
before you get it through
your thick skull?
And what makes you think
you can give gum to a cat--?
--[SAKAMOTO gasping]
--[HAKASE laughing]
[SAKAMOTO]
Would you cut it out?
I'm sorry.
[SAKAMOTO] Listen up.
As I've explained before,
I'm older than you in
human and in cat years.
And as your elder,
I deserve respect...
in the... form... of...
the title "mister"...
So, uh...
You gotta... do the thing.
You know... what I said
before... about the...
...you know, name and the...
[gasps]
[SAKAMOTO]
What?
Can I go and use the potty?
[SAKAMOTO]
Yeah! Sure! Go ahead!
[HAKASE]
Potty time!
[SAKAMOTO]
And she took it with her.
As I suspected,
those two kids are the only
ones living in this place.
Now I get it.
That explains why they're
so undisciplined.
[SAKAMOTO] So, if I'm
older than both of them,
I guess that means I'm the
oldest in the entire house.
Heh. So be it. Seems like
I'll have to step in
as the parental figure
they're lacking.
[SAKAMOTO] Hm? This is
quite the unusual family
I've been brought into.
Oh man, this thing
is so much fun!
[door slides]
Hey, Sakamoto.
What are you up to?
[SAKAMOTO gasps]
Crap! If she finds out
I was playing with an eraser,
she'll lose her respect for me!
The respect I worked
so hard for.
[SAKAMOTO]
I was, uh, taking a nap?
[HAKASE]
Cats sure do sleep a lot.
[SAKAMOTO] Anyway,
that's the way things are.
The way things are?
[SAKAMOTO]
Yup. Now you're getting it.
You've gotta get a grip
on the basics first.
Like... learning how to
respect... your... el... ders!
Oh man! This is so much fun!
[HAKASE laughs]
[SAKAMOTO gasps]
[HAKASE]
Ah! Sakamoto! Do it again!
Do it again! Come on,
the jump flip!
[SAKAMOTO]
Hey! Don't forget the basics!
I told you to call
me "mister" Sakamoto!
[NANO]
I'm home!
[HAKASE]
Hooray!
[IZUMI gasps]
[yelps]
--Don't you ever knock, Mom!
--[screaming]
[BOY A]
Green light!
Red light!
[BOY A]
Green light!
[YUUKO humming]
[YUUKO] It's like she
begging me to make a joke
about how she's
reading weird stuff.
Well, I guess
I'll take the bait.
That book your reading
is going undercover!
Yuuko.
Please don't ever make a
joke like that one again.
Uhh...
The jokes you make
are always so good.
My own aren't nearly as funny
when compared to your jokes.
Uhh...
[laughs]
Well, I don't always come up
with the jokes on my own!
Sometimes, the jokes
come up with me!
Y'know! Like just now
when you had your books
stacked up weird, it's almost
like you were asking for it!
But, like. Thing is...
I wasn't sure you'd
think it was funny.
Really, you weren't sure?
Are you being honest
when you say that?
Uh? Huh...?
I figured that you
would understand.
Huh?
[MAI]
I thought you'd catch on
to what I was doing since
you're so intelligent.
[gasps, laughs]
I had no idea you saw
me in that way!
I mean, I'm flattered you
think so highly of me!
And it's so good to know
there's someone out there
who thinks I'm trustworthy.
[MAI]
Trustworthy?
I'd rather not bring
trust into this.
And I don't think we should
speak to each other.
After all, we aren't
friends anymore.
[YUUKO]
Hm?
We're best friends.
We don't need words
to convey our feelings.
[gasping]
[YUUKO]
You mean it?
Come on! Don't be silly!
Even though we're best friends,
we can still talk, right?
[gasps]
[YUUKO]
But... Mai...
I would prefer it if you didn't
touch me so frequently.
Uh. Um.
All right then.
Sorry.
Please stop it.
You keep saying things like
that and I can't help it.
Huh?
[MAI] I can't stop myself
from liking you even more.
Huh...?!
Um, uh, hey,
it's not a big deal!
Of course you like me!
Because we're friends!
Best friends, right?
High-Five!
[MAI]
No, it's not like that at all.
[YUUKO]
Huh?
I do like you as a friend,
but I also like you like
you as more than that.
[YUUKO gasping]
[MAI] Sorry. I just...
can't really explain it.
Well, I... That's, uh...
[screaming]
[YUUKO]
What the heck is going on?
I knew something was up!
She's talking way
more than usual!
Come to think of it, she
was the one who suggested
that we go somewhere
alone today!
[YUUKO gasping]
[YUUKO] Did she want to
confess her feelings?
But why, and since when?
How long has she felt this way?
Hey, uh, Mai, I just have a
little something to clear up.
Uh. The thing is,
I don't know what to say!
This is all happening so fast,
and we're both so young,
and we're only in high school!
We've got our whole
lives ahead of us!
I think we might be
rushing into things!
You know that I was
just kidding, right?
[YUUKO] That was super, ultra,
great, delicious, wonderfully
hard to understand!
Why would you do that?!
You totally had me going there!
Now you're saying
it was all a joke?!
I see.
Uh...?
You're usually so perceptive
to these kinds of things,
so I was expecting that
you would figure out
what I was up to
and play along.
Well, I...
I had a feeling you were
up to something.
You're a liar.
Not exactly. I knew that
something was off,
it just took time for my
brain to process the signs.
I almost had you
figured out, too.
You ended up dropping the
act before I could put it
all together and start
playing off of you.
Didn't you just say that I
totally had you going earlier?
Huh?
I hate being lied to
more than anything,
so you can stop making excuses.
[YUUKO]
Uh...
Sorry.
Chill out I'm still just
joking with you.
[YUUKO] I don't even know
what to believe anymore!
So you didn't notice then?
You couldn't catch
the other joke I made?
[YUUKO] I don't care,
just tell me what it was!
It was at the very
beginning when I said
I thought you were smart.
You went along with it, so I
just kept on messing with you.
[YUUKO]
That was why?!
Well, at least I can understand
why you made that first joke.
[APARTMENT]
It's me!
Your friendly neighborhood
apartment complex!
Can you believe I'm
over 40 years old now?
I guess you could
call me the land lady.
That's got a raunchy
ring to it, doesn't it?
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 5.
Look forward to it!