[DOLPH humming]
[humming continues]
[knocking]
[DOLPH]
Hm?
[SOLDIER #53]
I've brought him, sir.
Enter.
[ALBERT growls]
[chuckles] Why, if it isn't
the great King Albert.
[ALBERT growls]
Why you...
Tell me, what's the
meaning of this, Dolph?
[DOLPH chuckles]
Oh, calm yourself.
I simply hoped we could
enjoy a meal together.
[ALBERT growls]
[inaudible]
[gasps] Well, that's a shame.
It seems as though there is
no more food left for you.
[laughing]
[growls]
[DOLPH]
Restrain him.
[SOLDIER #19]
Sir.
[ALBERT growling]
[DOLPH]
Huh...
So that's what you were after?!
[laughs]
Now, what do you say we end
this game of hide-and-seek
with that princess
of yours, King Albert?
Well? Your Majesty?
[ALBERT growls]
[DOLPH laughs]
[STARLA panting]
[SOLDIER A]
Did you find her?
[SOLDIER B]
Negative!
[SOLDIER A]
I'll check this section.
[SOLDIER #16]
Listen closely, men!
We're only after
the wooden cube!
Try not to kill the princess!
[ALBERT] Don't think for
a single moment you'll
get away with this,
Dolph. Hear me?
[DOLPH laughs]
I already have.
I'm afraid nobody has the power
to stop me at this point.
You're out of allies,
and out of luck.
What a shame. Right, Albert?
[laughing]
[ALBERT grunts]
[DOLPH] Thank you for this
little globetrotting trip
of yours. It was the most
perfect opportunity
you could have given me.
With the help of
my subordinates,
I was able to trap you
and the princess!
But why? What brought
upon this betrayal?
It looks like you still
don't understand at all.
I'm grateful for
everything you've done.
Raising an orphan like
me as one of your own,
and even appointing me as the
commander of your kingdom.
I don't understand.
[laughs]
Are you really this foolish?
It's because I have
my own ambitions.
[growls]
This is the kind of divine
punishment that you deserve.
Accept it.
[SOLDIER #16]
Lord Dolph!
Huh?
We've located the princess!
Okay! Let's boogie!
Excuse me.
Take this time
to think carefully
about your dying
words, won't you?
King Albert.
[ALBERT growls]
You filthy traitor!
What do you think
you're doing?!
Have you all completely
lost your minds?
[DOLPH] Well, if it isn't
Princess Starla herself.
It's so good to see you.
[STARLA]
Dolph, you bastard!
You have no freakin' idea
what you've done, do you?
[laughs] What a shame to ruin
that pretty face with
such a dirty mouth.
Of course I know what I've done.
I've taken King Albert's
precious wooden cube.
And once I get my hands
on your cube as well,
I'll be able to revive
the ancient weapon.
Then I'll finally
be able to ascend
as the new King of
the Fey Kingdom!
[laughs] Struggle all you wish,
but no one will save you.
There's nowhere to run anymore!
Now, hand it over peacefully
and I might let you live!
[DOLPH groans]
[gasping]
Whoa. Dolph is dead!
[SOLDIERS gasping, chattering]
Hurrah! All hail
the Princess, hurrah!
All hail the princess, hurrah!
All hail...
[BOTH]
...the princess! Hurrah!
All hail the princess, hurrah!
[SOLDIERS]
All hail the princess, hurrah...
You bastards!
[SOLDIERS scream]
You guys all owe me big time!
[SOLDIERS sigh]
[SOLDIERS chattering]
Now, then! Bring me to
my father right away!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[SOLDIER #8]
Hm? Wait a sec.
Isn't this the item the princess
was protecting earlier?
Yeah, then that must mean...
[SOLDIER #8]
Uh? Wait... what?!
[SOLDIER #8 gasping]
Then, that means...
I could have the
power to be king!
No, hang on,
let's not get crazy here.
Man, I could really
use a cigarette.
[SOLDIER #8]
After 12 long years of service,
I honestly thought
I would live out
the rest of my
life as a soldier.
But now... To have
a chance like this...
[SOLDIER #8]
I could never.
I have no reason
to become king.
I wouldn't know what
to do if I did.
And even with both cubes
in my possession,
I couldn't revive that
ancient weapon if I tried.
No!
[YUUKO]
Wha--?!
What a beautiful morning.
[YUUKO]
All right! I won! I think?
I did! Awesome!
Check it out! I just
won a 100,000 yen
in this lottery prize thing!
Really?! You gonna treat me
to a cut of that or what?
I don't even know what to
treat myself with first!
What do I even buy? Like a
car or a house or something?
Hang on a sec.
This, uh, is from last year.
[YUUKO]
Uhh...
Don't sweat it, the lottery
is almost impossible to win,
so it's fine.
[YUUKO] I know, but it
still breaks my heart.
Don't be like that.
You shouldn't be so down
on your birthday, so here!
Huh? For real? A present?
Thanks so much!
Can I open it now?
[MIO] Mm-hm. It's really
nothing special.
Just something that I had
laying around the house.
I'm sure it's great!
A gift is a gift!
It's the thought that counts!
[TAKASAKI]
Miss Sakurai?
Huh?
Oh, Mr. Takasaki!
How are you this morning?
I'm fine, thank you. So, um...
What are you gonna do
about that Aioi kid?
She never even attempts to
do her assigned homework.
Oh, uh! I, uh... I'm sorry!
I think a nice, stern lecture
from her teacher-slash-counselor
would help set her straight.
Uh, sure. I can try.
I'll see if there's something
I can do for her.
Now if you'll please excuse me,
I have a class.
[TAKASAKI]
I'm counting on you!
Excuse me.
[TOMIOKA gasps]
I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
I didn't spill any
on you, did I?
[sighs]
[TOMIOKA]
No, no, I'm perfectly fine.
Don't worry about it!
[TAKASAKI]
I just want to protect her!
In my 26 years on this Earth,
I've always had absolutely
no luck with women.
But now, feelings for
her have sprouted
like a surprise bamboo
shoot in the garden.
[gasps]
[TAKASAKI]
No, I can't! I'm a professional!
There's no room for romance
in the workplace!
I have to pull myself together!
[TAKASAKI]
Hm? Huh. Is that...?
Miss Sakurai!
[IZUMI]
Hm?
Wait, you forgot
your black folder.
[IZUMI] Oh, thank you
so much Mr. Takasaki.
Uh. But I have my
materials right here.
[TAKASAKI]
Uh.
[TOMIOKA]
Mr. Takasaki!
Where do you think
you're taking my folder?
Uh! M-My apologies.
[IZUMI] Heh! Well then,
I have to get going.
[sighs]
[TAKASAKI] I wish I could
take her mushroom picking!
Come to think of it...
Does she have a boyfriend?
She doesn't wear a ring,
so I can assume that
she isn't married.
Does that mean I might still
have a chance with her?
I don't even know what
kind of music she likes!
What's her favorite animal?
And favorite sport?
And vegetable?
Ah! What am I thinking?
Be gone, impure thoughts!
I can't be a role-model
to the students if I let
my mind wander like this!
Ah, Mr. Takasaki! Let me guess,
you're having trouble
with some of your students.
[TAKASAKI] But you know,
it should be fine
to ask what her
favorite food is.
Hey, Miss Sakurai, what's
your favorite thing to eat?
[IZUMI]
Um, I like a bit of everything.
[TAKASAKI]
Ha, ha, ha! Is that so?
How do you feel about
shiitake mushrooms?
They're great grilled or boiled!
[IZUMI] That's true.
And fried too, right?
[TAKASAKI] Of course!
Fried is perfectly okay!
[IZUMI] I bet those
would be pretty tasty.
[TAKASAKI]
Yeah, I got this!
Just act natural. It'll be
fine if I just talk normally.
Like if I'm talking to
eggplants or something.
Nice and calm.
[TAKASAKI]
Miss Sakurai?
Yes? How may I help you now?
I'm sorry for bothering you
so suddenly like this.
I was just wondering if you have
a boyfriend at the moment.
[TAKASAKI]
What the hell am I saying?!
I'm a fool! A complete idiot!
An absolute moron!
Nope! Um. I'm single.
[IZUMI]
Single... Single... Single...
[TAKASAKI]
Sprout! Sprout!
Sprout! Sprouting!
[IZUMI]
Um, Mr. Takasaki?
[gasps] I'm so sorry if
that was too forward!
[IZUMI laughs]
[TAKASAKI]
It worked out all right!
And I wish you the best of luck
with your next class,
Miss Sakurai.
Thank you! I wish you the
same as well, Mr. Takasaki.
Thanks.
Right, excuse me then.
I'll see you later!
[IZUMI]
I wish you the same as well.
I wish you the same as well...
[TAKASAKI gasping]
Well, I see that you're
in good spirits today.
[FEMALE VOICE]
Helvetica Standard.
[SHINIGAMI]
Wait! Please!
Give me back my sickle!
[TENGU A] If I don't pawn
off this sickle for food,
I'll die from starvation!
[TENGU A panting]
Oh no, a dead end!
[TENGU A yelps]
[SHINIGAMI gasping]
[TENGU A]
Well, I'll be.
[SHINIGAMI]
Please give it back to me!
[TENGU 3A]
Oh, man!
[BOTH] ♪ First comes a rock,
what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors
and a one, two, three! ♪
Wow! I won!
[gasps]
Oh hey, thanks!
[SHOPPING HOST A]
And that's not all!
[FOOD HOST 7A]
Add the coconut milk.
[WEATHER HOST 7A]
For tomorrow's forecast.
[ANIME CHARACTER 7A]
Miracle's in a pinch!
But I've got more
where that came from!
Hey, I bet you I can name
something that you've
never ever, ever thought about
before in your entire life!
Sure, go ahead.
A quirky office lady's
travel diary!
I have a bit.
[YUUKO]
Uhh...
[bell chiming]
[YUUKO]
Hurry!
Looks like the train is gonna
leave at any second!
[GIRLS panting]
Wait! Hang on!
[YUUKO]
All right! We're in!
Safe!
[MIO laughs]
You're the only one who made it.
[laughs]
[YUUKO gasping]
[YUUKO]
Selamat tinggal .
[CHEF 7A] Right. Um. Let's
keep those orders coming in.
[CUSTOMER B]
Yellowtail, and a Hamachi!
Let's keep those
orders coming in.
One tuna and a fluke fin please.
An eel for me.
So, one order
of albacore, and...
Heh. I forgot the rest.
[BOTH]
Wow, he forgot it all.
[CHEF 7A chuckles]
Huh?
[gasping]
[YOSHINO laughs]
[NANO]
Hm?
[screams]
Oh, hello there!
Huh? Uh, yeah, hi?
What do you think you're doing?
Uh. Heh, heh...
[yelps]
Hey, do you mind?
Why do you keep doing that?
I can't help it! That thing's
so cool and weird!
Huh? What? No, it is not!
It's normal! Keys are a very
popular trend right now.
Huh.
[laughing]
[screams]
[YOSHINO] How'd you pull
that one off, huh?
C'mon, what's your secret!
I just wanna see it! Chill out!
Okay. Fine. I'll go.
--[YOSHINO] Bye.
--[NANO] What?
Oh, come on, I was just
messing with you!
Well, I didn't care for it.
So can you please
give me my arm back?
[NANO]
Huh?
Pick a hand!
[NANO]
It's in your bag!
Hey! You got it!
All right, question number two.
Huh?
If Kenta's mom goes out
to the supermarket
and picks up ten apples,
and then eats three of them
later that day, and gives four
of the remaining apples to
her neighbor Yumiko then
where would you find
your missing arm?
In your bag!
Oh, wow! You got
another one right!
All I want is my arm,
so can you just...?
Only if you get the answer
the final question!
If you want this arm,
then you gotta earn it!
But why? It was my arm
in the first place!
Do you want it back or not?
Yeah, of course I do.
Then let's get started.
First, try saying the word
"bag" ten times fast.
[YOSHINO]
Hm?
Bag, bag, bag, bag, bag,
bag, bag, bag, bag, bag.
What kind of cloth would you
use to clean up a mess?
A bag! No, wait, I mean a rag!
Boop! Boop!
Huh?!
The correct answer was a towel.
No way! That's so unfair!
[YOSHINO laughs]
I'm just playin'.
You're good.
Okay, now can you stop
following me around?
All right, I'll stop.
Don't worry.
[YOSHINO]
Heh.
Huh. Would ya look at that.
[NANO screams]
Heh, heh.
[gasping]
[NANO]
It came off!
Finally! It came off!
I'm free!
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
Mio!
[MIO]
Hm?
Hey, I'll walk with you.
Okay. Are you on your
way back from class too?
[YOSHINO] Yeah, Oh, I just met
the most interesting person!
[MIO]
Really? Tell me about 'em.
[YOSHINO]
Well, her arm came off.
[MIO]
Huh?
[YOSHINO]
And she had a key in her back.
[MIO]
What?! No way!
[YOSHINO] I'm not kidding!
That's how she was!
[MIO]
Sounds pretty weird to me.
[WORD-TIME NARRATOR] I want
people to look at me and think,
"Oh, he looks pretty cool!"
Hey! You ready, Nano?
Okay!
[HAKASE]
Magic ball!
[SAKAMOTO]
Well, she is just a child.
Not surprising.
--[SAKAMOTO gasps]
--[HAKASE] I win!
Aw man, I lost!
[SAKAMOTO]
What are they doing?
That is not how
you play this game.
Sakamoto! How many
points did I just get?
[SAKAMOTO]
What?!
'Kay! It's my turn
to throw the ball!
Go!
[SAKAMOTO]
She hasn't even pitched yet!
[SAKAMOTO gasping]
[SAKAMOTO] Is she trying
to kill me with that?
Sakamoto! How many points
did I get for that one, huh?
[SAKAMOTO]
Oh, come on!
She swung again!
You're up. Go get 'em, champ.
[SAKAMOTO]
How do you expect me to do that?
There's no way hold that
bat in these little paws!
Aww...
[SAKAMOTO]
Unbelievable.
You'd think you would understand
how paws work at this point.
Since you're poking at
my pads all the time.
You kids can be so
simple-mind... ed...
[SAKAMOTO grunting]
[NANO, HAKASE]
Aww...
[SAKAMOTO]
Uh, okay then. Mew-ving on.
The way you kids are playing
isn't safe, so, I uh guess
I'll just have to sit here
and keep an eye on you.
Why don't you just put
the bat down and play catch?
--Sure!
--You got it, coach!
[SAKAMOTO]
Coach?
Coach, what do we do if
we only have one glove?
[SAKAMOTO] I think you'll
be fine without one.
Hey, coach! This glove
doesn't fit my little hand.
[SAKAMOTO] It goes on the other
hand like you had it before!
[NANO]
Help us, coach!
[HAKASE]
C'mon, coach!
[SAKAMOTO] Huh?! What would
you kids do without me?
[NANO]
Hakase! Here comes the ball!
Bring it!
[NANO grunts]
Oh no, where on earth
could it have landed?
[YUUKO] And then the teacher
totally freaked out at me!
[MIO giggles]
Can't blame him.
[MAI]
Agreed.
You guys really think so?
I think he went a little
overboard, personally.
[MIO] Yeah, maybe, but you
gotta watch out from now on.
[YUUKO]
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It could only get
worse from here.
Oh, thank you, sir.
[VOICE OF GOD]
A true gentleman!
[YUUKO] So, do mind
if I borrow it from ya
sometime, Mai, please?
[MAI]
Sure.
[YUUKO]
Great! You're the best!
[MIO] I wonder if that's
the girl my sister met?
[YUUKO]
...man I'm starving!
[YUUKO grunting]
[CUBE]
I am a Wooden Cube.
My master can only obtain
the ancient weapon
of legend by using
my power. [laughs]
The next episode of
My Ordinary Life is Episode 8.
Look forward to it!