We need to segregate the girls' and boys' areas.
We should move the boys' tent somewhere else,
and then make the girls' off-limit to the boys.
I don't know.
What would that solve?
If that's what you want,
then you guys should move it yourselves.
'Cause I'm sure as hell not gonna!
We weren't even asking for your help, jerk!
Hirata, you would help us move it, wouldn't you?
Yeah, of course.
I'll do it, but I think that
it's gonna take a little while.
I have no objections to
separating the boys from the girls.
But, while he's in the process of moving it,
Hirata would have access to both
the boys' and girls' areas, right?
Yeah, and what's your point?
I don't think he can be trusted to do it by himself.
Hirata isn't like that!
Well, he is a boy, nevertheless.
We should add another guy to the tent detail.
That will double the manpower effectively,
and the other benefit is that the
two boys can keep an eye on each other.
But, that won't work.
There's no way we can trust
any of the boys besides Hirata.
There's someone else.
And it's him. Ayanokoji.
Well, that's wonderful. Trusted by default.
Look at it this way, it's a compliment from Horikita.
And Karuizawa thought it was a good idea, too.
Well, I wouldn't put it quite like that.
Your girlfriend said that I was pretty much invisible.
I didn't raise any red flags.
Hirata!
Sorry, could you come here for a minute?
Uh, yeah, I'll be right there.
I can handle the rest of this.
You go ahead.
Sorry. Thanks for your help.
The boys' tent is officially moved.
Can you talk for a sec?
Class D seems to be having trouble.
I guess we've all got our fair share of problems.
Regardless of the reason behind it, as
a girl, I can't abide underwear theft.
It's perverted. Unforgivable.
Who do you think was responsible for it?
You thought it was me, didn't you?
I'm an outsider, so naturally, you all suspect me.
Sudo's not the only one.
That's the truth. Just look at them.
They're over there, glaring at you.
Of course he is.
Why shouldn't they all be wary of me?
If I were in the same position,
I wouldn't trust me, either.
For what it's worth, I trust you.
Wow. Thank you.
That was honestly the last thing I expected you to say.
I was only telling you the truth.
Looks like I'll be dining by myself tonight.
How's it feel, getting forced into menial labor?
You've got some nerve.
If it weren't for you butting in, it wouldn't
have happened, and I could have lived today in peace.
What was I supposed to do?
I couldn't trust Hirata by himself.
I needed you as insurance.
You know what?
Not everyone is hiding some evil side.
Some people are open books.
I guess that's true.
Take me for instance: I have nothing to hide.
But, still.
Most people'd do anything to keep the
world from knowing their innermost thoughts.
I know that's how you work.
And, because the virtuous are
often the most hypocritical,
I think I'm wise not to trust him.
Then why don't you just come clean, already?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come on.
You haven't been feeling well since the test began.
You don't have to hide it from me.
I feel perfectly fine.
Hypocrite.
You better get your hand off me.
Just stop moving.
Almost 38 degrees Celsius. Huh.
What are you, a thermometer?
When we all met up on the ship before the test,
I asked where you'd been. Remember what you said?
Yeah, I told you that I'd been in my room, reading.
You weren't resting in your room because you felt sick?
This could hurt our score.
Do you plan to tell the others?
I've already held out for five days at this point.
If I tell them about it now, it'd be for nothing.
I thought it might rain overnight,
but those clouds look ominous.
I wish we had a boat or something.
A break from the sun is kinda nice, though.
There are some dark storm clouds
coming in fast from the southwest.
Weather's gonna get bad.
Get ready for things to take an ugly turn.
Huh.
What?
Oh. It's nothing.
We'd better hurry up and gather
food before it starts to pour. Right!
And I'm about to gather up a storm, uh, no pun intended.
Ike's become pretty reliable.
You'd better step it up if
you wanna prove your usefulness.
Yeah, same to you.
We've got a lot to gather.
If we're gonna secure a day's rations
for everyone, we've gotta work fast.
Duh.
So, why are we still standing around talking?
Let's see. Fruit, fruit, fruit.
Where's the fruit?
Is there something bothering you, Kushida?
I'm just thinking about Ayanokoji and Horikita.
They've always been close, haven't they?
I wonder what it is about the two of
them that lends itself to such intimacy.
That's true, now that you mention it.
Are you ready to do this?
Okay, let's spread it out.
Hey, Horikita.
What is it now?
This is important.
It's about the class's key card.
What are you doing to take care of it?
I keep it on me at all times.
Then, when it's time to renew the spot,
I do it with the other students surrounding me.
As was agreed upon.
As for Ibuki and the other classes,
there's no reason that they would be able to identify me.
Would you mind if I took a quick look at it?
Here? Seriously?
It would actually be best for us to do it here.
Taking it out at base camp is risky.
I guess, but still.
Why do you want to?
What's the point of it?
Here's the truth: on the first day of the test, I saw
a student holding what I thought looked like a key card.
A Class A guy.
The thing is,
I have no way of knowing if it
was, in fact, a real key card or not.
'Cause I've never actually
seen one of them up close before.
That's true.
What you saw wouldn't be positive proof
if you didn't have a reliable point of reference.
Well, then?
Dunno. I still can't say.
I thought I'd know for certain after I saw it myself,
but the color might be
different. I'm not sure.
It's also possible that the school gave
each of the classes different color cards.
Yeah.
Hey, check this out!
Having a little private chat?
You're a bit too close!
Why you gotta leave the rest of us out of it?
Welp, I guess now I have to call you Muddykita!
Hey! Why would you do something like that?
C'mon. Now her boyfriend's
supposed to defend her honor. Y'know?
Right, Ayanokoji?
Ow. Hey, what--?
That hurt!
Oh, Horikita. You're covered in mud!
We should get you cleaned off right away!
Yeah, you're right, I can't stay like this, can I?
Horikita.
Were you trying to kill him?
If I hadn't reacted, you could
have split Yamauchi's head wide open.
Only two fish?
I can't believe you survived that!
Man, she's terrifying.
Maybe we should take a dip in the river,
since we're such a mess from working.
We won't be able to use the shower for a million years.
Yeah, the girls from the foraging team
have called dibs on it for a while, huh?
Who knows when they'll be done.
Dang, look at that line, man!
Huh.
Horikita?
Um, Ayanokoji.
Uh. Do you think you could come
take a walk with me for a minute?
We can't talk freely here.
What is this about?
You wanted me to go into the forest with
you and search for more food, or something?
Horikita?
Listen. I was careless.
I tell you this with full knowledge of my mistake.
Is that clear?
Mistake?
Something was taken.
Wait a minute.
You're not telling me that your
underwear was stolen, too, are you?
No, it's much worse than that.
What I'm telling you is...
The class key card was stolen.
I don't think we should tell anyone.
For right now, let's keep it to ourselves.
Just until we know the extent of things.
Yes.
If everyone else found out, it
would throw them into a panic.
And that's the last thing we need to happen now.
I have two suspects in mind already.
It's either Karuizawa, or Ibuki, which is more likely.
Are things really that bad
between you and Karuizawa?
In ways someone like you would never see.
Ways that were inevitable.
If you say so, but I seriously doubt it was her.
She's been in line for the shower
since before you went to clean up.
You're sure about that?
Yeah. Saw her with my own eyes.
Well, then. Ibuki's the culprit.
We should find the right time, and then ask her flat out.
Worst case scenario would be if
she took it and ran off with it.
That's true.
I'm so sorry.
I think it's best if you head back first.
I can catch up with you a little later.
Sure.
It's an unbelievable failure.
I bet she's so miserable she wants to crawl off somewhere.
Huh.
Hurry, someone bring us some water, quickly!
Good idea!
Damn!
She looks shocked. Does this
mean she didn't do it, after all?
Someone set the manual on fire?
Who would do something like this?
I found a fire extinguisher!
Step back. I'll put it out!
If it's not one thing, then it's another.
Why does this keep happening around here?
Does it mean we have a traitor
in class who's turned against us?
Why do you keep assuming it's one of us?
This is nothing like the stupid panty theft thing.
We don't know that!
Maybe you set it on fire to distract us from it!
Don't be stupid!
We'd never do something like that!
We're not dumb enough to start a fire in the forest!
--Everyone, just calm down. -- Why would we ever
believe the lies out of the mouth of
some nasty, underwear-stealing pervert?
None of us stole your underwear!
Obviously, the perverts stick up for each other.
What's wrong with you?
You keep calling us perverts,
but maybe you're projecting!
Looks like it's about to start pouring.
I hate this. You people are the worst!
I can't believe I have to be in class
with a panty thief and an arsonist!
What, are you deaf or something?
No one in this class took that stupid underwear!
Hey, has anyone seen Ibuki lately?
What? She isn't here, either?
Huh? She was just here a minute ago, I swear.
That sure seems suspicious, right?
Yeah, it's definitely suspicious.
Are you saying that she started the fire?
Do you think that means this whole time she was...
I knew she was a spy this entire time!
And now she ran away? Damn that girl!
Not good.
Anyway, we can deal with that later.
Now, Hirata, what should we do?
Uh... Hirata?
How could... this happen?
I've done nothing to deserve this.
How could someone...
Who would be so vindictive?
This is just malicious.
Hirata. Ike asked you a question.
Raining.
You should help the others out.
The clothes are still hanging on the clothes line.
Yeah, you're right.
We need to go put them away.
And we'd better get out of the rain, too.
Girls, start bringing all the clothes in from the line.
Boys, you go cover up the firewood.
It's useless if it's soaked through.
Come on. Let's hurry!
Right!
That just leaves...
She couldn't have gotten very far.
Took you long enough.
The underwear theft and the arson-induced panic.
It's odd how much trouble Class D has now.
What of it?
Don't play dumb with me. You're a hostile outsider.
You know we suspect you.
Do you have the proof to back that up?
Unfortunately, I don't have any solid evidence.
I can't tie you to the underwear theft.
But I'm not dumb.
We both know that you're the culprit.
That's not a very nice thing to say.
Why don't we settle this the easy way, right now.
Give me back what you took from me.
I don't know what you mean.
My limbs feel so heavy, and I'm hot.
No, am I cold?
Things aren't looking very good for me.
But I don't care.
I'm gonna tell you one more time.
Give it back to me right now.
Take whatever you want.
Hey. You're fast.
You could get disqualified for doing that.
Disqualified by whom? No
one's here to see it. Anyway.
I think you came looking for a fight!
Nice. You've done this before, haven't you?
If I can't get it back, I'll let
Class D down in the worst possible way.
I looked down my nose at all of them.
Called them worthless and stupid.
When, all along, at the end of the day, I'm useless.
A failure, resorting to violence. It's pathetic.
Just admit it was you.
You're the one who stole the key card.
Since you've worked so hard, I guess I'll tell you.
Yes. I'm the one who stole your precious card.
I expected to have to work a
lot harder to get it out of you.
You can't say I used violence.
There's no proof. That's too bad.
If I got that card,
I could analyze your fingerprints.
And then I could prove that you stole the underwear, too.
If I can just get her off balance.
I've been convinced of this for a while.
I thought for sure you were involved in it somehow.
The fire at the camp earlier.
Why do you think I would be
so evasive when talking to you?
I just wanted to confirm my suspicions about you first.
Do you mean...?
I've gotta go.
I have another appointment now, you see.
This was a nice talk. But it's over.
Oh, the item that you requested?
I got it for you.