Earth and water might impede us in our
escape from this wretched labyrinth prison.
But, the sky is free!
You see, even in the darkest depths,
there remains a glimmer of hope.
Oh, Father.
You've built such splendid wings.
But will they carry my weight?
Can I soar freely?
Above everything?
My Icarus. You must listen to me.
Freedom can addle the mind, bring delusions and fears,
and arrogance can lead one to death.
Even the birds fly with...
Now, this is an egregious waste of tax dollars.
A few days ago, a man, whose name I
won't mention to you, contacted the school.
"You must expel Kiyotaka Ayanokoji immediately," he said.
Well now, I wonder what his angle might have been.
I hope I'm not supposed to know who it was.
But we both know you can't
expel me without good reason.
You're right.
As long as you remain a student at this school,
the rules protect you from that injustice.
Of course, if you were to cause any trouble...
That's a different matter altogether.
Watch me, Father!
Sorry to inform you.
But, unlike our arrogant hero, Icarus.
I do not intend to challenge
the sun. The sun. It's so near!
Your intentions are irrelevant in this case.
If I decide that you've become a problem,
then a problem is what you are.
Is that a threat? Because it sounds like one.
Not a threat; it's a trade.
If you don't wanna get expelled,
then try to ascend to Class A.
And as long as you do your best,
I will cover for you, unilaterally.
A good deal by anyone's standards.
Icarus!
Maybe, but I'm not going to take it.
In that case, Ayanokoji.
You're going to lose all of your freedom.
You're going to be expelled.
Gods of Olympus.
I beg of you, put a curse upon me!
How dare you.
You call yourself a teacher?
It would be wise to make your decision with haste.
Will you try to make it to
Class A, or will you get expelled?
Curse me! I beg of you!
Trying to manipulate me is not gonna work.
You're going to regret your actions.
Don't worry about me.
My life is so filled with
regrets that one more won't hurt.
Throw away my freedom,
to protect my freedom?
The eternal summer ocean!
The wide blue yonder!
On a ship, in the middle of the Pacific!
Now this is what I call cruise paradise!
Look at that view!
Makes your heart race and steals your breath, doesn't it?
It truly is an incredible sight!
Aren't you glad you didn't get expelled after all?
Yeah. This trip feels like a dream.
I can't believe we go to a school that's so generous
they take us on a nice cruise for no reason at all!
Yeah!
The luxury cruise ship Speranza .
Onboard, you'll find a four-star restaurant.
A live theatre venue.
Pools and other various amusement facilities.
There's even a first-class spa.
If I were to purchase a ticket as a private citizen,
it would cost me a few hundred thousand.
Wow!
We can borrow any of these cute swimsuits for free?
Hey, Kikyo!
Wouldn't this bikini look so fierce on you?
Um, it's a little revealing, don't you think?
Aw, come on, we're on vacation.
Live a little!
Heads up, Kikyo! Coming at ya now!
Got it!
I'm doing it.
I'm finally gonna tell Kushida how I feel!
What?! A-Are you serious?
If I don't, I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
Can't have that.
Ike.
Go do it, then.
Okay! Here goes nothin'!
So, what is it? You okay?
I was wondering.
Hm?
May...
May... May... May...
May I please have the extreme honor
of calling you by your given name?
Well. Please don't keep me waiting.
Would you allow me to call you Kikyo?
Yes, but only if you allow me
to call you Kanji, in return!
Uh, Kanji?
Kikyo! Kikyo!
Kanji, please!
Whaddaya know. He pulled it off.
All he did was call her by her first name.
Ayanokoji!
You've got to tell me Horikita's given name!
Huh?
Tell me Horikita's first name
right this second, or I'll go crazy!
I think it's Suzune.
Suzune. It's beautiful. Lovely.
All right!
I'm gonna go find her and call her Suzune.
Hi, Suzune.
Suzune, can you talk for a sec?
Suzune, you wanna take a walk with me?
Airi. Airi. Airi. Airi. Airi. Airi. Airi.
What is their problem? This is weird.
Heh. I'm beautiful.
Whoa, is this place free to everyone, too?
Do ya think they would send us a bill for it later?
Well, people from all the other
classes are eating, so it's probably fine.
I think we should go somewhere else.
Okay, where should we go?
Welcome.
Would you gentlemen like a table for four?
Uh. Sure.
Hey, what kind of food is this, anyway.
Look, they have French: "Fro-mage de teh-teh?"
With a delicate, aromatic herb reduction?
Look. No worries.
Let's just order whatever, 'kay? Hey, over here!
S'cuse me!
Can we order some food already?
Hey, dudes!
You're all from Class D, aren't you?
Yeah. And what about it, buddy?
A bit of advice.
This fine establishment isn't
intended for garbage like you.
What?!
Trashy people should be eating trashy food.
Get yourselves some burgers and fries.
What the hell do you have
against burgers, you little punk!
Yahiko.
Cease with these ridiculous provocations now.
But, Katsuragi...
Despite the fact that we're on vacation, we
could still lose points for unsavory behavior.
Please conduct yourself in a
manner befitting a Class A student.
Uh. Yes, sir.
You lot would also do well to mind your manners,
and stop being a nuisance to those around you.
Huh? What did we do, exactly?
Uh!
He's the one who assaulted
those poor guys from Class B.
He's got crazy eyes!
I hear he's actually killed people.
Really?
Gimme a break, you guys!
Repeating your mistakes?
Do you intend to get yourself into trouble again?
Don't get worked up. Let's go.
Katsuragi, from Class A.
Yeah, there we go.
Um, Ms. Hoshinomiya?
Sorry, sorry. Go on. You were saying?
I think Sakayanagi and Katsuragi from Class A,
and also Ryuen from Class C--
they're the ones we should be keeping an eye on.
And what about in Class D?
Well, Horikita and Hirata, for sure.
I feel like there's someone
else from Class D, too, though.
I've heard rumors that
Koenji has really good grades,
and his athletic abilities are
apparently amazing, but I don't know.
No, it wasn't Koenji.
I know that much.
Are you thinking of Ayanokoji?
Yeah! There's something about him.
My gut says to watch out. He's on my list for sure.
But, Ms. Hoshinomiya, I can't
just go on your gut instincts alone.
You're such a meanie!
A few days ago, a man I won't
mention, contacted the school.
"You must expel Kiyotaka Ayanokoji immediately," he said.
Hirata?
Sorry. Did I wake you up?
No.
Good, I'm glad.
I'm about to go hang out with
Karuizawa and a couple of her friends,
so do you wanna come with me?
Karuizawa?
I'll pass, thanks.
I don't really know her, or any of her
friends, now that I actually think about it.
This might be a good opportunity.
No better time than the present.
Does he honestly care about my social
life that much? Or is it something else?
Ayanokoji.
The truth of it is, there's something
I wanted to ask you to help me with.
You want my help?
Would you be willing to act as
a liaison for me and Horikita?
I think if we want to unite
Class D and make progress,
well, she'll be an integral player in making that happen.
So that's what this is about.
I've heard she's great.
That she's the one who proved Sudo's
innocence, and that was no small feat.
If we could work togeth--
Shouldn't you answer that?
Sorry. I guess I'd better get going.
If you change your mind and wanna join,
just call me and I'll let you know where we are.
I'll do that.
Cool, later, then.
Hello?
Sorry. I'm on my way.
Sir! Please wait!
We'd prefer that you dry off before
walking on the carpet if you don't mind!
Sorry to break protocol,
but I've never toweled off
after swimming in my entire life.
Sir, please listen to me!
So, would you say that I am,
"dripping with beauty" or "manliness"?
Beautiful!
Sir, I'm begging you!
This is exactly what I deserve.
You sure got here quickly.
I did. What did you summon me for?
To ask you a question.
Do you believe they'd just give us a holiday?
I'm sure there's some kind of catch.
Go on.
I think we're heading to an island.
The school owns it, and there's a boarding
house on it big enough for all the first-years.
When we get there...
We can't let our guard down for a minute.
They're watching us.
It would appear that I have found you at last.
You set up decoy cameras in the special annex.
That was a clever little prank you pulled, missy.
Sorry, I don't know who you are.
There's a special place in my
heart for women like you, Suzune.
I don't know how you accessed that information,
but I've never given you permission to use my given name.
That's a nice expression.
I think it's incredibly sexy.
Like I said, I don't know you, and I don't want to.
I find your presence repulsive at best.
I'm just one of your devoted fans.
How dare you!
Next time, I'll deal with you personally.
I'm so looking forward to it.
Ryuen!
Oh, Ibuki, it's you.
I need to have a talk with you right now.
Heh, heh.
Missed me so much you had to see me?
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm fed up with the way you
operate, and I won't stand for it!
I see. That's all right.
We can talk about it later in my room.
Just you and me.
Albert!
You're going along with this?
I see you've officially become Ryuen's guard dog.
Get back here right now, Ryuen!
I'm not finished talking to you!
Let me go!
That's enough.
Hey. Are you okay?
It's none of your damn business.
Class C seems to be on the verge of collapse.
That's my full report.
I hope it's enough.
Thank you for all of your thorough
and diligent work, Ms. Masumi.
What should I focus on now?
Good question.
I want you to investigate some students.
Which ones?
That's check.
So that's what I've been thinking.
How do you feel?
Um, would you ever want, well, um, want to d--
d-date--
Sakura?
What's wrong?
Um. Hi. Uh.
How long have you been standing there?
I literally just got here.
Did you...
Did you hear what I said before you spoke?
No.
Thank goodness.
Why?
Oh, um, I just...
Uh...
Is something going on with you?
No! No.
Nothing bad is going on with me, exactly.
But I'm having trouble making
conversation with our other classmates.
So, I'm sorry for asking for your help with it.
Don't be sorry.
If you just need someone to listen,
that's something I'm happy to do.
Thank you so much!
Sure.
It's not like it's that big of a deal.
Huh? Is that Ayanokoji and Sakura?
See you later.
I'm going back to my room.
Wait, come back!
I'm sorry.
I wanted to say hi, but I should have left you two alone.
'S cool.
I guess Sakura still hasn't
overcome her fear of strangers.
What a beautiful, starry sky!
Right? It's pretty. Don't you think so?
When Kushida displays behavior like this,
it's easy to forget.
She was like a different person that night.
Well, I'd better get back to my room.
Are you done for the night already?
Yeah, I'm gettin' very sleepy.
Sounds good.
I guess I'll see you tomorrow, then.
Have a good night!
Yeah, thanks, same to you.
Hold on.
Kushida?
You're wary of me now, aren't you?
I knew you were.
I can always sense that sort of thing.
Sorry.
When people leave me all by myself, I get kind of lonely.
I thought that maybe you were...
Never mind, it's nothing.
Forget about it!
Good morning, students!
Time to rise and shine!
Our island destination will soon be in view!
We hope you'll take a few minutes to bask in
the sight of this highly significant scenery.
Don't let the moment pass you by!
Significant scenery?
Dang! Get a load of it!
Good morning! Isn't this so exciting?
Yeah. Good morning.
It's simply breathtaking.
Don't you think it's beautiful, too, Ayanokoji?
The usual Kushida.
By the way, have you seen Horikita this morning?
Why ask?
I thought she would be with you.
I haven't.
She doesn't quite seem like
the type to revel in a vacation.
So she's probably in her room.
I bet you're right.
As we make preparations to disembark on the island.
We'll brief you on what you can expect once we dock.
Until then, you're required to wait here.
It's so hot. I wish they'd speed things up.
Have you been in your room?
Yes. I was reading, what of it?
It was extremely engaging, too.
But, since we're not allowed to bring our
personal belongings, I won't get to finish.
Anyway, what is this?
We'll confiscate your student IDs.
In their place, you will wear these wristwatches.
Those who take them off without
permission will be severely penalized.
They're all acting especially cautious.
Like they're on high alert.
I agree.
I can't imagine they'd go this far
if we were just here for a little fun on the beach.
I'm Mashima, the instructor for Class A.
To begin with, I'd like to express my
gratitude that we all made it to the island.
Almost all of us.
One of you won't be able to join because of an illness,
and that's a real shame.
Without further ado,
I'm glad to announce the beginning
of this year's special examination.
Huh?
Special examination?
The duration of the test is one week.
You'll live as a group on the picturesque
desert island you see before you.
You are your own responsibility from here on out,
so you're expected to behave accordingly.
Now! The test of survival begins!
Looks like vacation's over.