I've always had trouble interacting with people.
I can't even bring myself to look them in the eye.
It scares me.
That's why I hide.
I use my mask to cover up my real self.
That way, it's harder for people to hurt me.
I'm okay being by myself.
It's safer that way.
I'm okay being lonely.
I can get over that feeling.
It's hot in here.
You're right,
and intense heat usually causes people to be irrational.
Which makes it the perfect place for a set-up.
Sudo'd be less likely to keep a cool head.
So, then. Have ya come up with a stellar plan yet?
I'm in the brainstorming phase.
Sakura's testimony bought us time.
But we won't always be so fortunate.
I just wish we could find some more
substantial evidence to seal the deal.
Oh, speakin' of which, this area doesn't have any.
Security cameras.
That's true.
If there'd been cameras, well,
then we would have all the evidence we need, wouldn't we?
Indeed.
On the other hand, if this area did have them up,
those jerks would never have
summoned Sudo here in the first place.
What's the matter?
I think I've come up with a plan.
Sakura?
Oh, hey.
Good morning.
Oh. Um...
Yes, good morning.
What's wrong?
You don't have to testify again,
you know. The hearing's private today.
So, there's no need for you to be so tense.
Okay.
And anyway, we have a plan.
If it works, we'll be able to save the whole class.
You're the one who made that possible.
I want to tell you that I trust you.
So if you ever happen to find yourself in need of help,
just ask for me, and I'll be there.
I appreciate that.
And I'm not the only one.
I'm sure that everyone in class trusts you, too.
Horikita, Kushida, Sudo, all of them.
Yeah.
Um. Listen.
I've got something on my mind.
There's really not much you could do to
help the situation, but I thought I'd try.
I'm sorry, Sakura.
I hate to cut you off,
but is there any way we could talk about this later?
Yeah.
So damn hot!
Why the special annex?
What do you guys think Kushida
wants to talk to us about, anyway?
I bet she's gonna ask me out!
Yeah, right, keep dreamin', ya big dummy.
Ah! Not so hard, jerk!
Let me go!
Huh?
Uh!
What the hell?
What are you doing in here?
You were expecting Kushida?
Huh?
That email she sent was just a ruse.
I told her to send it to you.
And why would you do that?
I wanted to have a chat.
It was the only way to get you here.
But, I'm glad I finally have your attention.
Listen, last time we got summoned here was
when Sudo beat us up. You know that's the truth.
Sudo needs to take his punishment like a real man.
We're out of here.
I'd stay if I were you.
If you leave now, you'll regret
it for the rest of your lives.
Do you really want to ruin your futures like that?
And what the hell is your problem, lady?!
Whatever.
Maybe you should be more observant.
What are you even talking about?
What's the matter?
You seem a little shaken up.
Is that a... security camera?
There's a science laboratory in the special annex.
They work with all kinds of hazardous chemicals
in there, so, of course there would be cameras.
But, how?
Wait a minute.
If there's footage from those
cameras of what happened in here,
they'd know Sudo's innocent and wouldn't
need to have a hearing in the first place.
And you would definitely have no
reason to tell us about it, either.
The moment that the incident took place,
both parties were doomed to
suffer some form of punishment.
Regardless of why, the truth is that Sudo beat you up.
That is an indisputable fact.
Oh, so that's why we're here.
You guys would also be hurt by the camera recordings.
Of course, Sudo is still going to be punished,
but what you three did could get you all expelled.
You told a malicious lie and
got the whole school involved.
What did you expect would happen?
Oh, yeah?
If that's true, then why hasn't
the school said anything to us?
The school has a habit of testing its students.
They want to see if we can work
out some sort of truce on our own.
That's why they're taking a hands-off approach.
They want to see what we'll achieve
with the extra time we've been given.
I want you all to think back on the hearing yesterday.
Don't you think it seemed like
they already knew everything?
No way. I can't get expelled.
Ishizaki! Why don't we tell them we made it up.
If we have a solution,
maybe they'll be more lenient and not expel us!
What are we even supposed to do?
Shut up, you idiots!
Don't be too hasty in making your decision.
You know there is a way to save both of our classes.
If you're open to hearing it.
Like hell there's a way, jerk!
Why not take the entire incident off the table?
It's quite simple, really.
If you three would only withdraw your complaint,
it will be like nothing bad ever happened.
If no fight occurred here,
then how can the authorities punish anyone?
All we have to do is get our collective story straight,
then the school can't pursue it any further.
So, do we have a deal?
Hold on a minute.
I just have to talk it over with someone first.
Hey!
What's the matter, can't make
up your mind without your master?
Give it back!
How pathetic.
You bitch--
Resorting to violence?
Go ahead. Try it.
Dammit!
Ishizaki. Just admit it, we lost.
Let's accept Horikita's offer.
We can't afford to get expelled, dude!
Fine.
We'll take everything back.
Someone help.
You have my word that I'll pay back the points
I borrowed from you yesterday, with interest.
Let's discuss the terms.
You got it.
An eye for an eye, a lie for a lie, right?
Glad I could help.
I never expected someone with a mind like
yours to be in Class D. I don't understand it.
Well, Horikita came up with the Machiavellian scheme.
I'm just some guy following orders,
to be perfectly honest with you.
Uh-huh.
Well, if you say so!
Sakura?
Hey, what's up?
Ayanokoji, help!
Shh! Be quiet.
Did you... Did you read all the letters I sent?
You've got to know how I feel about you, my darling.
Right?
So, why?!
Why have you been avoiding me like this?
If you know how precious you are to me,
why are you treating me this way?
You know how much I love you, right?
Someone help me...
So if you ever happen to find yourself in
need of help, just ask, and I'll be there.
Uh?
Let me go right now! Ah!
Dammit!
Listen.
If you don't let me do what I want,
I'll put the real you on the internet for everyone to see.
You wouldn't like that, huh?
Huh? What's going on?
Why are you looking at me that way, my darling?
Stop! Stop looking at me like that!
Stop it right now!
No! Let me go!
I'm going to show you just
how much I love you, darling.
I know you'll learn to love me, too, Shizuku.
You'll understand after this. Just be quiet.
We are destined to be together.
I know you feel the same way.
Local electronics store employee
caught in the act of sexual assault.
You're gonna be famous.
No, infamous is more accurate.
W-Wait a minute!
That's not what this is!
By all means, explain.
Remember, security cameras don't
lie, so be careful what you say.
Even if it was just an attempt,
she's still an underage girl.
With that on your record, you
would certainly lose your job.
The press is cruel.
They might even go after your family.
Face it.
As of this moment, your life is over.
You think you can get away with
committing such a heinous crime?
Something like that would never fly here.
--Come quietly... --Let me go! She loves me!
I didn't do anything wrong!
You can't interfere with our love! It's destiny!
I'm Shizuku's number one fan!
She wants me, too!
Everything she does is because
of how much she cares for me.
She only updates her blog to show me her new pictures.
Why can't any of you see that?
She loves me, she just won't admit it!
She even came to this school so she could be close to me.
Shut up. I don't even know you!
What? What's the matter, Shizuku?
I want nothing to do with you.
A fan wouldn't treat me like this.
Monster! I never want to see your face again.
I can't believe this.
You're a dirty liar.
You're ugly. This ugly bitch tricked me.
I'll make you pay for this!
Come on! You owe me an explanation, bitch!
I never could love an ugly, lying bitch like you!
Do you hear me?!
That's quite enough of that.
Damn you.
Damn you!
I'm sure Ichinose and the
cops can handle it from here.
I'm glad I had your contact info.
That's the only way I could have found you.
See? There you are.
I'm so sorry. I really am the worst, huh?
I thought I could make it on my own, but I can't.
Being an idol comes with its own set of hazards.
But I am grateful for one thing.
You guys. I'm so happy.
You like me for me.
I'm done lying. Sorry I didn't tell you before.
You have no reason to
apologize,but in the future,
if you want to talk to me about
anything, I promise I won't dismiss you.
I appreciate it.
Ayanokoji, um.
The look in your eyes.
I've never seen it in them before.
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing at all.
What do you want?
You called me out here to talk, so talk.
I'll get straight to the point.
How did you do it?
Sorry? How did I do what?
Don't play dumb.
We both know those imbeciles wouldn't
withdraw their complaint for no reason.
I'll leave that to your imagination.
I'll rephrase the question, then.
Who came up with the brilliant idea?
What made them back off?
I don't know. Why does
that even matter to you?
If you're truly serious about advancing to Class A,
then allow me to offer you a simple word of advice.
Learn as much about Ayanokoji as you can,
while you still have the opportunity to do so.
Otherwise, before you know it, it'll be too late.
Hey, Ayanokoji!
How'd the hearing turn out?
You'll never believe what happened.
The guys in Class C, they
backed off for no apparent reason!
I see. That's incredible.
I know, isn't it?
Do you think Horikita pulled some strings for me?
Yeah, probably.
She's awesome. But also kinda weird.
Well, I gotta go. See ya!
What is that supposed to mean?
Why do you imagine Ayanokoji would be
going out of his way to help the rest of you?
And why, despite his superiority,
does he refuse to reveal what he's capable of?
I don't know.
To put it in the school's terms,
Class D is the place for those with defective qualities.
The ones who barely had the chops to get in at all.
It's just my opinion, so take it with a grain of salt.
But out of everyone in Class
One-D, the most effective student
is Ayanokoji.
Uh.
The students from Class C
wanted to withdraw their complaint,
and against my better judgement, I allowed it.
Oh, did they, now?
It's a strange world we live in, I guess.
Are you trying to prove a point?
That Sakura is not in fact the
fabricator everyone thinks that she is?
Well done, sir.
Your little sister is the one behind all of it.
I didn't do anything, really.
Tachibana. We have an opening for a secretary?
Yes.
Well, then.
You just say the word, and the
secretary position on the council is yours.
What? Are you serious?
Do you object?
No. I was just making sure I understood.
I have no objections to that.
Ayanokoji.
Please join the student council.
No, thank you.
I don't like expending more energy than I have to.
The student council seems like too much work.
And honestly, I just want to have a normal life.
I accept that for now.
Ayanokoji.
It would be in your best interest not to disappoint me.
Which one of you was it?
Who withdrew the complaint without consulting me?
We... We're all responsible.
Well, Albert.
Sorry, boss's orders.
I've got no beef with you.
My plan was to get one of those idiots
expelled, to see how the school would react.
Now, I'll have to find another way.
You're all worthless.
It's entirely reasonable that
you should suffer for your sins.
Give me the names of the ones
who set you up, and Al will go easy.
Sakayanagi?
I recognize you. You're from Class C, aren't you?
It appears you think you've already been crowned
queen of the school. Well, that's just adorable.
I never intended to be queen of anything.
I'm going to crush Class D, and then Class B.
And before it's said and done,
I'm coming for Class A, too.
Do you really think you can make that happen?
There can be only one ruler here.
I couldn't agree more!
It's a relief that your little plan worked, isn't it?
You manipulated me, didn't you?
Admit it.
What do mean by that?
You pointed out the lack of cameras in the special annex,
which then led me to plant the false
evidence and bear all of the risk.
Nah, you're just overthinking it.
You made a promise to me.
You said that you would help me advance to Class A.
Yeah, only after you virtually forced me to.
Hold on.
I'm not quite finished with you yet.
I want to know what's going on inside your head.
What you're thinking.
Well, I just want to live my life in peace.
Is that so hard to understand?
You wouldn't help me if you didn't want to, deep down.
Yeah, you're right, I suppose I just
wanted to help a friend out. Ya happy?
That's a lie.
You've never cared about your friends, and you know it.
Who are you?
Really. What's your game?
Line up!
I will help you get to Class A, like I promised.
But...
But, what?
Don't go prying into my life.