Man:
Your attention, everyone.
Having won all of her games
thus far in the tournament,
Kurami Zell
awaits her next opponent.
Is there anyone left
who is up to the challenge?
Stephanie:
Sora, wait,
you can't be serious.
You're gonna crash
the coronation?
Hey, I just scored
a new life in this world.
I can't lose my place
to live that quickly.
Stephanie:
Yeah, but‐
Now then, I think it's time
for me to become king
and take back
our lost territory!
( theme song plays )
If there are no other
challengers,
I shall proceed with the former
King's final wish
and crown Kurami Zell
as our new ruler.
Should anyone wish to protest,
speak now‐
Sora:
Objection!
( crowd gasps )
You heard me!
( annunciated ) Objection!
( chuckles )
So, are you saying
that you request
to be her next challenger?
Yep.
( crowd gasps )
Despite your loss, you're still
desperate enough to win
that you're sending
your butler after me?
In case you hadn't noticed,
Little Princess,
this isn't a playground.
Yeah, and it's not the place
to hand over the throne
to some con artist either,
especially one
who's getting help
from another country.
( all murmur )
Sora:
Well, Shiro?
Shiro:
There's one.
Anyone else
hiding their ears?
Nope.
Kurami:
That strange device,
they used it before.
And just what
do you mean by that?
Oh, come on now, let's say,
for example, if the crown
was given to someone
in cahoots with the Elves,
Elkia would be pretty much
screwed, right guys?
( all murmur )
What exactly
is the meaning of this?
So what, is this
your pathetic attempt
at accusing me
of cheating?
Calm down. I clearly
said "for example."
Or maybe it actually rings
a bell for you, huh?
Fine then, since
you've made your objection,
I suppose I'll have
to humor you with a game,
is what you want?
Yay! Thanks, Madam.
I'd really appreciate that.
But, but Miss‐
One thing,
if we're playing poker again,
maybe this time, you should ask
your friend to leave.
I'm sorry to have
to do this, but...
There's an elf here!
What the hell's going on?!
So these two witches
were working together?!
Nothing to say?
The pretty swindler's gonna
abandon her partner in crime?
How cruel.
I get it.
So you've teamed up
with some random elf
to try to make me out
to be an enemy of Imanity,
is that it?
(chuckles)
Pretty good deflection,
I must admit.
Perhaps it's best you left.
Elves have no place here.
There.
You satisfied?
Sure am.
Ready to play now?
As you're likely aware
as stated by the pledges,
I get to decide the game.
But no need to worry.
I'll choose a game
where cheating is impossible.
Pledge number five,
the challenged party
has the right to decide
the content of the game, huh?
Dang, no poker this time?
Well, since
I'm such a nice guy,
I won't bother asking
about your reasons.
Say cheese!
Hmm.
Wow, you're not really
photogenic.
If you smiled once in a while,
you'd be a lot cuter.
We'll hold the game
in another venue.
I'll call for you
once it's prepared.
Stephanie:
Wait, you're telling me
she used magic to beat me?!
Hey, will you keep it down
a little bit?
That's right,
Shiro and I both noticed
when we saw your game
at the tavern.
Don't you mean
I noticed?
Don't sweat
the small stuff, Sis.
So that's what
it does then,
that special secret tool
of yours
is for detecting magic,
isn't it?
So how'd they do it?
What kind of magic
did that Elf use?
No idea, sugar pants.
( yelps )
Magic's amazing, isn't it?
If you could change cards
when they're face‐down,
we could never prove it.
Sora:
Under normal circumstances,
there's essentially
no way to beat her.
Shiro:
Why do you think we didn't
challenge her before?
Look, Steph, I'll break it down
as simply as I can for you.
Sora:
First of all, this round‐robin
style tournament to become king
is pretty jacked up
to begin with.
Let's say a country partners
up with an Imanity
with the promise
of becoming king.
From there on, they can
manipulate the games.
They'll play against
other Imanities
who also can't detect magic,
so it's a guaranteed win.
Now that they've got
a puppet king,
they can pretty much do
whatever the heck
they want with Elkia.
The plan's so simple,
even a baby
could've dreamt it up.
But then, guess what the other
countries start thinking.
So what do you think
we should do now?
Kurami:
There's nothing to worry about.
He's just another Imanity.
Even if he's probably getting
help from another race,
so am I.
It's not like
I didn't expect this.
Kurami, do you really think
you'll be able to handle
playing the games
without me?
Kurami:
(scoffs)
I'll be fine.
Stephanie:
So you really think
it's possible that Kurami
has convinced herself
that we're getting help
from another race?
Sora:
Yeah, by now
she probably realizes
that Elkia is caught
in a diplomatic war
between other nations.
Steph:
Then we're in luck.
She can't use magic again
since she'll think
other races will be watching,
ah‐ha!
So she'll have to play fair
and square,
and it'll be impossible
for her to cheat using magic!
(groan)
It's all sunshine
and flowers in your head!
Just crush my optimism,
why don't you?
I'm sure they expected it.
Another country
was bound to intervene.
But I'll bet this time,
they'll use some spell
or mind trick
we can't detect.
If we can't even spot
their regular tricks,
then we're totally doomed.
They'll lay out a game
that looks fair on the surface
so it doesn't seem
completely hopeless.
But they won't use
their magic directly on us,
like screwing with
our vision or memories,
because it'll be too obvious.
In other words,
it won't be completely
impossible to win.
So is that supposed
to make me feel better?
As long as there
is some path to victory,
no matter how small...
Then you can bet your sweet
fanny that Blank won't lose.
There you go.
( chokes )
Hmm?
Kurami:
Let me be honest with you guys.
The only reason I struck
a deal with the Elves
was to secure a place
for Imanity to live
after I've won the tournament.
Once we've acquired
a fair amount of territory,
I'll cut ties
with the Elves for good.
Sora:
Oh, jeez.
Shiro:
I know she's dumb,
but you didn't have
to say it out loud, Sis.
So you know,
we might be spies,
and yet you're still
telling us your plan‐ cuckoo!
Think about it,
the only way for us to survive
is to win the right
to live under the protection
of a powerful nation,
give up on games,
and close off our borders.
There's no other choice,
right, Little Princess?
You of all people
should understand that.
Well, I‐
Kurami:
What's more, Elven Gard
currently comprises
the largest nation
in the world,
and not a single race has been
able to defeat their magic.
It's impossible
for you to beat me,
so it's in your best interest
just to withdraw from the game.
I swear to all Imanity
that I won't let
the Elves make me
their puppet.
Sora...
Okay, not a bad plan.
We live quietly under
another nation's wing.
Sounds pretty promising.
Doesn't it?
That's why you should withdraw‐
But I refuse!
You know one of the things
Blank loves best?
Both:
Telling people "no"
and shutting them down
when they think
they've already run the game,
then telling them
they can go screw themselves!
Number four
on our list of things
we always wanted
to say someday!
Sweet, we did it!
Yeah, we're so awesome.
It appears that reasoning
with you is a waste of time.
Then just as you wish,
I will make you yield by force.
It's your funeral.
But, Sora, why not?
Why what?
That plan she was
just talking about,
it kind of makes sense
given the desperate
situation we're in.
(sighs)
Steph, look, don't you think
it's about time
you learned to stop being
so trusting of people?
For one,
what proof do we have
that anything she said
is even true?
Second, if she's so confident
that she can win,
then why did she ask us
to withdraw?
And third, even
if anything she said was true,
I could be a spy
from another country,
and anyone dumb enough to spill
their plan shouldn't be ruling.
Okay, fourth, if we play along
and she does any digging on us,
we're totally screwed,
comprende?
Wow, you really
put a lot of thought
into that speech,
didn't you?
(sighs)
Look, those are just details.
Don't sell humanity short.
We're better than that.
Chess?
That's right,
but this isn't
your normal game of chess.
Each piece
has a will of its own.
Give them orders,
and they'll move.
Think of them
as your own personal army.
( chuckles )
So that's how this works.
Shiro, what's the plan?
Chess is no different
than a game of tic‐tac‐toe.
So, like, it's cool
if we rotate mid‐game right?
Sora‐
I'm not trying
to be difficult,
but the two of us count
as a single player.
Plus you seem to be pretty
familiar with this game already
whereas we don't
have a clue. Cheese!
Kurami:
They'll never figure this out.
You may do whatever you wish.
But why? Do you think
I'm going to lose?
Hey,
don't take it personally.
Hell would freeze over before
you ever lost a game of chess.
But this isn't
the game you're used to.
And don't forget, combined,
we're a single player.
Blank is both of us.
You're right, I know.
I'll be careful.
Let's go.
Right.
Finished
with your little chat?
I'll let you make
the first move.
And the game
is officially underway.
All:
Aschente!
Kurami...
D‐2 to D‐4.
Sora:
Chess favors
the first player.
If both players
always pick their best moves,
then the first player
has a higher chance of winning.
There's no way she's
not aware of that fact.
What the‐
it moved by itself.
G‐7, advance.
Stephanie:
But it moved three spaces!
That isn't fair!
Kurami:
Weren't you listening?
In this game,
the pieces have wills
entirely of their own.
( chuckles )
Now I get it.
The players' traits
affect their moves,
stuff like charisma and one's
potential leadership skills.
You're a quick learner.
It's the perfect game to decide
the next king, don't you think?
Knight, please
move to C‐3.
Now F7, forward.
Just "forward"?
That's kind of vague.
What kind of move's
that supposed to be?
Just shut up and watch.
Shiro:
E‐2 to E‐4.
F‐5, forward
to take her piece.
Sora: Let's not forget,
F‐5, forward
to take her piece.
once Shiro's deep into a game,
her concentration
is unbreakable.
Shiro:
Knight take H‐3.
That's how
even my little sister
has the power
to defeat a god.
Queen to H‐5.
Shiro:
Check.
Wow, Shiro's amazing!
Even with Kurami
sidestepping the rules,
Shiro's totally
destroying her.
It's not that amazing
when you think about it.
Sora:
Take a game of shogi,
for example.
It's entirely possible
for a top player
to defeat their opponent
using nothing
but their King and Pawns.
Simply bypassing
a few rules isn't enough
to defeat a true master.
F‐2, move to F‐4.
Sora:
However...
Shiro:
F‐2, move to F‐4.
Wait, why isn't it moving?
I knew this would happen.
Mind filling me in?
What's different
about this chess game
is that sometimes,
the pieces won't move.
Steph:
What?
Sora:
No soldier would willingly
put themselves in a situation
that would result
in their death.
They are either need
a fantastic leader
or extraordinarily
high morale.
Steph:
But that means‐
Sora:
Correct, she's incapable
of sacrificing
any of her pieces.
Kurami:
Better make your move.
Otherwise,
you're going to run out of time.
Now, knight, take H‐7.
A‐2, move to A‐3.
Bishop, forward.
Hurry and take out
the opponent's knight.
And Knight, take H‐5.
Shiro:
D‐4 to D‐5.
( chuckles )
Shiro:
(weakly)
A‐3...
Bishop...
I'm... sorry...
Shiro.
Sora, I can't do it.
( crying )
I'm really, really sorry.
Sora? Shiro?
Sora?
( inhales deeply )
Attention, all forces!
As your King, I hereby declare,
those who fight bravely...
(inhales)
will be heroes
and win the right to get it on
with any woman they like!
Also, all you soldiers fighting
on the front line, if we win,
you will be relieved
of any further military duties.
I'll make sure that you're
exempt from paying taxes,
and you'll be handsomely
compensated by your country!
Therefore, fellow virgins,
you must not die!
(wave crashes)
And to all of you
who have family
and other loved ones
back home,
I promise you will
all come back alive!
( all shout )
But wait, you can't really
promise them that!
Thanks to you,
I realized this game
wasn't real chess.
We gotta think of it
as a strategy game.
I'll take it from here,
but if I start losing it,
feel free to jump in, okay?
Now watch, 'cause games like
this are totally my specialty.
Attention,
Pawn Squad Six!
The enemy's moving
from the front line!
Strike first
and cut them off!
He can't do that!
Now cavalry squad two,
the pawns made an opening,
so move in!
King and queen, listen up!
Hurry and move your asses
to the front line!
Kurami:
Hey, wait a minute,
it's supposed to be my turn!
Sorry, but in a real war,
what fool waits
for their enemy's turn?
Pawn Squad, advance
and form a defensive wall!
Ha, see that?
Just a couple
of cowardly monarchs
hiding themselves
behind their own soldiers.
What kind of ruler
lets their men die
on the front line while
they sit behind and watch?!
Kurami:
Ignore him!
Listen, soldiers,
listen, friends,
this battle decides the outcome
of Elkia, of humanity!
The city represents the final
bastion for our people,
and the fate of everyone
now rests in your hands!
Open your eyes!
Do you honestly want
to risk your lives
and your people's future
by handing over the crown
to some shifty charlatan
like her?!
But if we come together and win,
then she will be your queen,
this girl who mere moments ago
gathered all of her courage
in her little heart
to march you towards victory,
this girl, who is crying
on the inside
because you wrongly accused her
of being a merciless tyrant!
And you bastards
call yourselves men?!
( all shout )
What is this?
Where'd this power come from?
Proud knights, bishops,
and rooks, now is your chance!
Prove to me that you live up
to your rank.
Give the pawns support
and crush the enemy's defenses!
This can't be happening.
It's impossible.
Should be, right?
I figured
you're using Elf magic
to force the morale
of your troops higher.
It would be easy
to just claim
you have more charisma
than we do.
Who wouldn't?
It's not like anyone
can prove it.
Unfortunately, you made
one giant mistake.
And what was that?
Throughout all of history,
the wisest of kings know
that an army will not obey
oppressive or tyrannical rule.
People will only fight for what
they believe is truly right,
and in this world,
there is only one thing
that is absolutely,
truly right!
What is he talking about?
The one eternal truth,
the one virtue to rule
the whole world is cuteness!
Cute is the world!
Our instincts and desires
are driven by it!
And for it,
we'll give everything!
Sorry, but that's just
the way us men are!
But that's... ridiculous!
Kurami:
I still don't know
which race is helping them,
so if I do this,
they might find me out.
But I have no choice.
Now, king,
move forward to E‐6!
What the heck just happened
to that piece?
Sora:
This is bad.
Everyone, retreat!
All forces, pull back!
The enemy's using
brainwashing magic!
Kurami:
He knows.
Can someone explain
this to me, please?
Sora:
Don't let the opponent
touch you.
Kurami:
Get the hell outta there!
They don't know
how I'm doing it.
(laughs)
As long as they can prove
that I'm cheating, then I win.
Now, all forces advance!
Sora: Oh, crap!
crap, crap, crap, crap.
I've royally screwed
this one up.
I thought she had only
one cheat up her sleeve
and disregarded
any other possibilities.
I can't believe I made
the same mistake
I was just lecturing
Steph about!
What, were the stakes not high
enough for me or something?!
I'm better than this!
(panting)
Sora?
Off with the enemy King's head.
Kurami:
Finish him, my Queen.
And that's... checkmate.
Queen, wait!
Wha‐ Sora!
Oh, my Queen.
I beg you,
put down your sword.
To me, you're...
...beautiful!
All:
Say what?!
My Queen, my dear love,
please search
deep within your heart.
Do you truly find
any value
in that so‐called
King's service?
She brainwashes her soldiers,
abusing and using them
like expendable tools.
Then she forces you
to lead the assault,
unworthy of your sword.
I beg you to reconsider this.
Please think of your people,
think of the kingdom
that you've sworn to protect.
( laughs )
When it comes to dating games,
there's nobody,
and I mean nobody out there
that's better than me.
Way to go!
Looks like we've got
their Queen!
He figured a way out!
Not yet.
Huh?
Shiro:
The enemy's
using some kind of magic
that lets them brainwash others
just by touching them.
Stealing one piece
from their side and adding it
to our ranks won't be enough
to change anything.
It won't?
Sora:
All right,
if a virgin like you
can sweet‐talk a chess piece,
surely you can find
a way out of this mess.
I caught her off‐guard.
Maybe if we wait,
she'll make a sloppy mistake.
No,
that might even be worse.
Maybe I should hurry
and make the next move.
Damn it, what should I do?!
I royally screwed
the pooch on this one.
How the hell
am I gonna fix this?!
Sora.
Shiro?
The two of us are Blank.
We'll... be... fine.
Kurami:
Stay strong.
Don't back down.
Now, knight,
I want you to advance
and eliminate
that traitor Queen!
Both:
That's it!
What's wrong?
Come on, move it!
( gasps )
Sora:
Jackpot!
This is how we're gonna win.
Shiro, you focus
on commanding the army.
Keep them moving
so we don't get brainwashed.
Piece... of... cake!
You finally have a plan?
Listen up, Steph,
you don't always
have to lift your sword
to fight a battle, understand?
Huh?
There's always
more than one way...
...to win a game!
( theme song plays )
Sora:
(wheezing)
Must I talk like this
if I'm going to be king?