That's kind of ridiculously overdone.
Why would they ever need to
build something so absurdly huge?
They couldn't possibly be trying to
compensate for something, could they?
Okay, well, this was a nice little vacation
but could you please take me far away from this place now?
Hey, wait, this embassy's on foreign soil.
Yeah, yeah, but it was originally
our castle, too, you know.
But this is an invasion of their territory.
Just relax, I made an appointment already.
Hey there!
Greetings, Lord Sora and Lady Shiro.
Welcome to our embassy.
I'm the assistant ambassador to
the Elkian embassy, Ino Hatsuse.
A pleasure to meet you.
Wait, when did...
This morning.
I could see the old dude checking me out in
the library, so I signaled to him I'd come over.
Man, just like they say, those
Warbeast senses really are awesome.
It's like they've got telescopic vision.
You could've told me about this, you know.
Undoubtedly the reason for your visit
is to meet with Ambassador Izuna Hatsuse.
Is that correct?
It looks like the rumors really were true.
The Warbeasts can read people's minds.
Glad to hear we're all on the same page.
Right, let's get moving.
Very well.
This way, if you please.
Forget about the Warbeasts.
How did Sora see him from way over there?
In case you hadn't noticed...
Uh...
The game...
it's already begun, hasn't it?
Hey, Jibril?
Yes?
What do you guys call this?
It's an image display device.
But wait, the Warbeasts can't use magic,
so I don't know how they're doing it.
My, but it is rather fascinating!
Cool.
What's going on? Why have the floor moving?
Pardon, but I beg you follow proper
procedures when making an appointment next time.
Due to an incident, many Warbeasts
harbor extreme animosity toward Elkia.
Since you arrived so quickly, most weren't
informed and may not act entirely... civil.
Well, that makes sense, I mean, a dog that
talks and walks is still just a dog, right?
Hey, Steph, what incident?
Yeah, he's referring to the Construction Wars.
Having a foreign embassy bigger than
our palace was really bad for our image,
so we ended up building a new bigger one.
That's the one we live in now, right?
No, 'cause after that, the Eastern Federation built
their embassy even bigger, so we had to keep competing.
But when it comes to construction technology,
Elkia lags way behind the Eastern Federation, so...
Isn't that ironic?
If I recall, the Warbeasts are only ranked 14
themselves, so looking down on Imanity is... well,
I'm not sure how your people say it, but we
say it's like a moron laughing at an imbecile.
That may be true in a sense,
but it seems a bit petty coming
from someone from the sixth order.
Speaking of which, as a weapon, I fear you're defective
if you're serving a bunch of shaved monkeys.
Okay, guess relations in this
world are pretty strained, huh?
The war dragged on forever,
and thanks to the ten pledges,
they can't get violent, so they ended up
letting out their aggression this way instead.
My lords, please wait here.
Each culture certainly has its own style, huh?
Master, you never told us how
you make contact with the Warbeasts.
Nobody's talking about it, so just take the hint, okay?
I apologize for prying, master.
But I can't read minds like the beasts here
and I really, really want to know.
Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell
me, tell me, tell me, tell me.
Hmm?
So even with your little magic rectangle,
you still couldn't see him clearly,
but you guessed that he saw you and
gestured to him accordingly, is that right?
Don't tell me you bluffed someone who can read minds.
I apologize for the wait.
Presenting the Eastern Federation's
ambassador to Elkia, Miss Izuna Hatsuse.
Erase time!
Pretty girl with animal ears, want to come play with me?
I'm a little bit of a perv, but I've got a clean record.
Why the hell are you assholes touching me, please?
What?!
Minus 50 cuteness points for sure.
Who said you shitheads could stop? Thank you.
You popped out of nowhere and surprised me is all, please.
Commence the petting, peasants, thank you.
Uh...
Adding "please" and "thank you" at the end of a
sentence doesn't automatically make it polite, you know.
Of course it does, you idiot, thanks.
I apologize if she has offended you.
My granddaughter's still getting
a grasp of the Imanity language.
Oh, and by the way...
Keep your filthy monkey paws off of her, you
hairless primates, or I'll rip you a new asshole!
Or that's what I would say if you weren't so charming.
So I guess she gets it from the old fart, huh?
He's a bad accessory. Minus 1,000 points.
But I just love her conflicting personalities.
Plus 1,050 points.
You hairless monkeys do that way better than grandpa.
Please, keep going. Thank you.
Look, why don't we give the whole monkeys thing a rest?
I'm Sora. That's my little sister Shiro.
Nice to meet you, Izuna.
Sora and Shiro, got it. Please, thanks.
Well, then, let us hear what you
feces‐tossing apes have to say.
I thought you could read our minds.
This is a place of diplomacy,
a place to exchange ideas.
Or is that too complicated for
you knuckle‐dragging gorillas?
Don't get pissed.
She just likes us better, Pops.
He's so immature.
Master, I advise you to be careful not to
shatter the Warbeast's fragile, dainty heart.
He's so pathetic, we wouldn't
want to hurt his little feelings.
Didn't anyone teach you people manners?
All right, gramps, I'll tell you what we're here for.
How about we play a game, and you
bet your granddaughter's panties?
And I'll put up Steph's for my bet.
Hmm?
If you wanted me to roll you in a rug and beat to
death, You Should Have Just Said So, You Damned Monkey!
What? You'd rather have Jibril's than Steph's?
Certainly, as you wish, my master.
Don't tell me you want Shiro's.
Come on, gramps, that's sick. She's only 11 years old.
No, don't tell me.
You don't want mine, do you?
Sorry, but I don't swing that way.
It's okay, Sora,
I'll protect your chastity.
Too many choices or what?
Her panties are a pretty good deal for you, old‐timer.
Please excuse me, but if you refuse to tell us
why you're really here, then maybe it's best...
Drop the pathetic act already.
Hmm?
If you can read thoughts like you say,
then I'd suggest you go for the panty game.
Look, I know it's not the panties you're after.
It's just a low stakes match, and a good chance
to wipe away all my memories about your games.
So let's shake on it.
Oh, second‐guessing, huh? Looks like I was right.
Smells to me like cold reading,
cheap parlor tricks that don't even
need the amazing senses of a Warbeast,
just some observational skills and a bit of intuition.
Coincidently, that just so
happens to be a specialty of mine.
Is he...
So you done confirming this isn't a bluff yet?
Now then, since we've established that
your so‐called mind‐reading ability
is a bunch of crap, let's get down to business.
Like why we really paid you a visit.
We, Sora and Shiro, designated representatives of
the 16th order of Imanity in the kingdom of Elkia...
Have blessed the Eastern Federation with the
opportunity to become the first honorable sacrifice
on our path to world domination.
Therefore, we hereby challenge you
to a game between nations.
And we demand everything the Eastern
Federation has on this continent.
A game between nations?
So you mean we're officially
attacking the Eastern Federation?
Did I really just hear you correctly?
Yep, and by the way, we're not changing our bet.
It's still for Steph's panties.
Should have just bet Izuna's
panties while you had the chance.
Sorry, Gramps, them's the breaks.
And that's a check.
Master, could you please
explain the madness going on here?
What's wrong, Jibril? You still don't understand?
Basically, we've got the Federation backed into a corner.
Over the last 50 years, their
technology evolved pretty rapidly,
and they grew more and more powerful,
but despite being so advanced, they're still an
island nation that needs resources from the mainland.
Before they could even set foot on the main continent,
Elven Gard attacked, or perhaps they were lured in.
Either way, no other country would agree to play an
unknown game that even the strongest nation kept losing.
The Federation couldn't get onto the continent.
They should have just lost so
more countries would challenge them,
but for some reason, they didn't.
Let's solve these mysteries in order, shall we?
Question one!
Why do they wipe all memories of the game?
If they don't, they won't be able to win every time.
Correct! It defeats the goal of luring others into play.
Even though it's not entirely logical,
they wipe memories because there's
something they're trying to keep secret.
But still, you can erase people's memories
but not the fact that they lost.
Question two!
Why'd Elven Gard challenge them four times?
They knew that they might lose, but they
wanted to figure out what the game was.
Unlike Elkia, Elven Gard is a really big country.
They were prepared to suffer
some losses to do their research.
After their first loss, they figured it must
have been a game where you couldn't use magic.
An Elf would think that was the
most likely reason they'd lose a game.
So they came up with some kind of countermove
and challenged a second time and lost again.
Then they played a third time.
I'm not sure how, but they figured something out.
So they went back to using their official cheats they
call magic and made their fourth and final challenge,
and they lost again.
That's quite an imagination you have.
In any case, I'm not too concerned with the way they lost.
What I want to know is why they stopped after four games.
If you think all that's just my imagination, that's cool.
I mean, you're old and kind of grumpy. I get it.
I see two options.
The first‐ they realized the game was impossible to win.
And then the Elves could've exposed the cheating and won.
Or second, they learned the tricks of the game
but could never figure out why they kept losing.
So that's why the Elves stopped challenging them.
But still.
Now that's odd. So what do we have here?
You were able to figure out the game,
but you have no idea why you kept losing.
Starting to get good, party people!
Time for question three!
What works equally well on these very different races?
What game would be a guaranteed win made
by technology only the Federation would have?
And the answer is?!
They made a video game where you can cheat all you want.
They made a video game?
What the hell is a video game?
I doubt that you'd know, Steph, but, Jibril,
you challenged the Eastern Federation once already, so how
come you'd never seen that thing at the entrance before?
Uh, well,
I guess that's because...
Because you'd forgotten it.
It's a memory associated with the game.
Still, despite all that, if a Flugel
like Jibril doesn't know anything about them,
it's pretty safe to say the Federation is
the only country in the world with video games.
You erased the memories to keep the games a secret.
Because guess what everyone in a
video game where you're the game master,
you can keep cheating your
ass off till the cows come home.
And your opponent, who's busy
running in circles, stays clueless.
Plus, if you don't even know what
cyberspace is, then magic's pointless.
All that mind‐reading garbage is just a
cover story so your opponents won't look closer
and find out you're cheating, right?
Hang on, we're almost done here.
So you can tell when someone's lying,
but there's no way you can read their mind.
And the final question is?
Golly!
How in the world were they able to figure all this out?
The answer's on the house,
pops. Do you care to take a guess?
Don't tell me it was the former king.
We made him swear by the pledges to tell no one,
but even he didn't realize we couldn't read minds.
No, that's not the problem here.
Right, that's not the real problem.
You made the former king promise not to speak
about the games to anyone, but since he did,
it proves you couldn't read his mind. How?
'Cause he pledged to tell no one so long as he lived.
That doesn't mean he couldn't tell anyone after he died.
So now that we know all about your devious game,
are you starting to get a little worried, Old Man?
'Cause if you're not, Gramps, we'd be happy to go
to the Elves and tell them all about your tactics,
and you'd be forced to play them all over again,
and you'd lose.
At this point, it's in your best
interest to erase our memories.
But if you're prepared to bet your
territory just for Steph's panties,
then I guess that means my imagination must be correct.
Damn it.
Then that means...
Your only other option is to claim
my theory is just a load of crap
and run away from our challenge, right, Old Man?
But you said you could run away?
I'll make it worth your while.
I'll throw in all of Imanity.
Huh?
And Imanity's race piece!
K‐Kurami? Why is‐
Listen, Fiel.
Do you know of any games in the past
where someone bet a race piece?
Of... of course not, never.
If you bet your race piece and lose,
then you also lose all your rights as an Exceed.
That means...
That the ten pledges no longer apply.
In other words, we're no better than animals.
It's like a death sentence for all of Imanity.
That son of a bitch!
Sora, are you insane?
I've bet our entire territory and put
the lives of all Imanity on the line.
If you try to back out now, that's like telling
the entire world that my imagination was correct.
Bet you didn't see that coming, did you,
Mr. Freakin' Mind Reader?
Check and mate.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Even if you're correct, keep in mind
Elven Gard still lost this game four times.
Plus you dare bet your precious race piece?
Do you want your people to go extinct?
Say, Old Fart,
remember when I flagged you down from the library?
Maybe if you'd thought about how we could do that,
you'd have realized that the
two of us are not from this world.
When it comes to video games, you can use as
many cheats or assists as your heart desires.
None of that will help you.
Blank will never lose to anything like that.
When we showed up here...
Did you really think we would
just roll over like easy prey?
Now it's your turn to be the hunted, Warbeast friend.
Who the hell do these two think they are?
Well, guess you can't agree to a
game of this scale on your own, right?
We can do this another day.
We're betting our race piece, so
all of Imanity has the right to watch.
The four of us are ready, and we're
not gonna let you squirm out of this.
But wait...
I don't really get any of this, thanks.
But, Sora, and Shiro, sounds like you
buttwads challenged me to a fight, so thanks.
A fight? No way.
Izuna, let's play a game next time, okay?
I won't lose to losers, thank you.
Sorry to disappoint, but you will.
Everyone knows, Blank never loses a game.
See you soon, Little Izuna.
You idiots, what the hell were you thinking?!
Do you realize what you've done? And what if you lose?
What the heck are you gonna do?
I don't know.
If we lose, we're pretty much
done for, so what else is there?
I know if we lose, it's game over
for us and three million people,
but if we win, we get the animal girls and their land.
Not too shabby, eh?
Isn't it so exciting, Shiro?!
It's so exciting.
What... What's wrong with you two?
Just relax, Steph.
It's just a game, right?
I knew it.
It was stupid and naive of me to entrust
these people with my grandfather's hopes.
If it bothers you, Dolly, then consider this‐
if the Masters win, every Warbeast on the planet
will be stripped of their land and also their rights
and possibly face death.
Who do you think should take responsibility for that?
We rule each other and kill each
other through games instead of violence.
The losers are exploited, enslaved, and killed.
That's the essence of the ten pledges,
being daring enough not just to risk your
own life but also the lives of all your people
just for the tiniest opportunity to defeat your enemy.
Those are the qualities we need in a ruler.
Huh? Say what now?
What?
Don't tell me you guys haven't figured it all out yet.
The way to win, the way to beat this world.
The way to win and beat this world?
Well, now I see why God gets so bored of this place.
Poor Tet. I feel sorry for him.
Don't worry, guys, we'll conquer the hell out
of this world as promised, the whole damn thing.
We won't lose.
There's no point in even
planning for that sort of outcome.
No chance of us losing, you got me?
And that's checkmate.
Come out here, you stupid kids!
My, how quickly their attitudes
have changed almost overnight.
How do you think you'd feel if you
were suddenly given a death sentence?
I think it's actually pretty
strange that they're acting this calm.
Are you going to do anything to quiet them down?
If they were that mad, they could
try and take the throne back from us.
It's just a bunch of whining,
and I doubt any of them have the guts to challenge us.
More importantly, what's the hold‐up?
It's been a week already.
You mean why the Federation hasn't
picked a date for the game yet?
With their whole country at stake,
I'm sure it will take some time.
Yeah, I figured as much.
I'll just wait for someone with
more of a backbone to show up.
Uh, huh?
Looks like they're finally here.
Kept me waiting long enough.
Yeah, of course I know what you guys want.
I'm ready when you are.
Shiro, listen up, 'kay?
You know that I believe in you.
Yeah, I know. I believe in you too, Sora.
Shiro, never forget the two of us are always one.
The two of us are bound by a promise.
Shiro, we're not the heroes of some stupid kid's manga.
Shiro, we've always won the game before it's even started.
Sora?
I'll get the last piece to beat the Federation, okay, Sis?
No! W‐wait!
Let's get this game started, shall we?
Sora?
Shiro, rise and shine.
What's the matter? Hey, what's wrong, Shiro?
Sora? Where are you?
Come help, please! You can't leave me here alone!
Shiro, who are you talking to? Who's this Sora guy?
Do you want me to go find him for you?
No way.
No way!
Shiro, is everything okay?
Steph?
Where's Sora?
Where is he?
My brother?
Brother?
You have a brother?
And his name's... what again?
I won't let go of your hand, Sora.
It would feel like my soul was leaving me.