And the first piece
makes its move.
What'll you do next?
Man: Query‐
Do you, "A,"
desire the destruction
of Imanity?
Or "B," have you finally
decided to take action?
Now, now, don't you dummies know
that eavesdropping on people
isn't very polite?
Man: Query‐
an event fluctuation
was detected just before
the new king was crowned.
We assume this heralds
your intent to join the battle.
Oh, you fallen gods
are a serious buzzkill.
You guys still think
you're so hot.
Well, listen,
Mr. High and Mighty,
Old Deus‐ First Order
of The Exceed‐
I'm not on anyone's side.
So you can just keep playing
your same boring games,
but they're coming.
They're coming all the way
to your front door.
( footsteps approaching )
Steph:
After seeing the way
those two rallied the people
of Elkia to their cause,
I felt like
they were our saviors.
Well, not anymore.
They just delegate
all their kingly duties
to me and the ministers
and then spend the whole day
sitting around playing games!
Today's the day.
Today's the day
I end this once and for all!
( theme song plays )
Hyah! Hmm!
( both groaning )
Sora:
My eyes!
Okay, you slackers,
time to get out of bed
and do your job as king.
( sighs ) Damn it!
I made sure this room
was hidden from the vile rays
of the morning sun!
It's after noon,
you dope.
36 o'clock is too early.
Is that watch even real?
Ugh, you tossed my precious
books all over the place.
Yeah, put them back in your
grandpa's room for me, okay?
( yawns )
Sora, as the new king,
that room is supposed
to be yours.
It's been that way
for many generations,
so you can't just decide
to move out of it on a whim.
Yeah, but the bed's lopsided.
It's hard to sleep in.
The floor is for champs.
Oh, no, you are not
going back to sleep!
I find it really embarrassing
to think that
you're the new king
who's been entrusted
with the lives
of over 3 million Imanity.
I'm embarrassing, am I?
Sorry to be a disappointment.
You're entitled
to your own opinion,
but hear this‐
Not in this world or any other
will Blank do any real work!
Don't underestimate‐
Both:
The will of Humanity!
If that's the will of humanity,
then we're better off
going extinct.
That's it.
My patience for your shenanigans
has finally run out.
Sora, I challenge you to a duel!
Oh...
so you want to play
a game with me, huh?
Sure about that?
Yes, that's right,
I would.
Okay, so pledge number five‐
It says here that since
we're the challenged party,
we get to set the rules
of the game.
Still in?
( hesitantly )
Yes.
B‐but as one of the greatest
minds in human history,
I'm sure you would never
choose a game
where you have an advantage
over little old me.
All right, fine, pick whatever
game you think you're good at.
And what are we playing for?
If I win, then you have
to become a decent person!
( groans )
Holy crap, if the
ten pledges are absolute
then they can even grant
crazy wishes like that.
In that case, Steph,
instead of making me respectable
just make me, like,
totally satisfied IRL.
I‐R‐what?
Why do I need to be respectable
if I can be content?
Go ahead, challenge me.
I'll do everything
I can to lose!
( shouts )
Sora, you're not allowed
to lose to anyone but me.
Wait, darling sister,
would you stand between
your brother and true happiness?
Blank can't lose a game,
no matter how painful
the cost may be.
( groans )
But it's impossible for me
to lose to Steph
in an honest game.
Whatever!
All right!
Whoa! Yes?
I'll bet on the tiny,
ridiculous, remote chance,
that somehow against the will
of the universe, you'll win.
( laughs )
Wow, you've really
gone and done it now.
In that case
the game I pick is...
Shiro:
Blackjack?
Okay, I'll be the dealer,
and you'll be the player.
Is that all right, Sora?
groans )
Well, at least try
to be interested!
( yawns )
At least try
to look awake!
Now look here, you, blackjack
is 100% a game of chance.
All your cheating
and dirty little tricks
won't help you this time,
understand?
Come on!
Say it with me.
Aschente!
Aschente.
Steph:
You fell right into my trap.
A game of chance?
Or so I'd have you think.
'Cause that's not
how I'm going to play.
Yes, that's right.
I've learned that
you can cheat
as long as your opponent
doesn't find out.
I've been practicing
this trick in secret
and I'm gonna use it to knock
your skinny butt down a peg!
Dearest granddaughter,
the weak must use their wisdom
to kick all
the skinny butts they can.
Such is the hope
of all humanity.
Steph:
Thank you, grandfather for
believing in our potential.
And thank you, Sora,
for teaching me
how to beat you with it!
Hit me...
Stand.
Well, I've got 21.
19 here.
( giggles )
I'm just getting started.
( sighs )
Well, it's time
for the final round.
Best of luck!
I think we know who's
going to be winning, though.
Blackjack is one
of the rare games
where the player has an
advantage over the dealer.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sora:
The dealer has
to draw another card
whenever he's below 17,
so he has a high chance
of going to bust.
But you haven't had
that happen even once.
That's some pretty
impressive luck.
I'll stand this turn.
Steph:
Has he just given up?
He didn't even look
at the cards.
Well, looks like
the game is over.
Yep, sure is.
( gasps )
In a natural blackjack,
you get back 2.5 times
what you bet.
That means I win.
Yay.
But I had humanity
on my side.
Grandfather:
Stephanie, my dear girl‐
Grandfather!
Don't you know
if your opponent is a human,
you're just screwed,
( echoes ) just screwed...
Hold on! What?!
Oh, what a hollow victory.
I didn't think of that!
Truly content people are just
an urban legend anyway.
I refuse to accept this!
How did I lose?
You must have been cheating.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
I thought you said that
blackjack was a game
of pure chance?
( grunts )
I used card counting.
Card counting?
I don't think I know
what that is.
Sora: You think
of the cards as numbers
and count them
in your head.
Cards between
two and six are +1,
ten and above are ‐1,
and seven through nine
are 0.
Easy peasy.
So you just count
the number of cards
that have been played so far
to mathematically find
the numerical probability
for what will be played next.
So you used math in a game?
I didn't know that
was even humanly possible.
Wait just one second!
Isn't that cheating?
No, cheating refers to
techniques
like the forced shuffle
you were doing.
You knew from the start?
Yep, and it made counting
that much easier.
Oh, impossible, he not only
saw through my tricks,
he used them to defeat me?!
Ow!
Hey, there,
where you off to?
Oh, just back to work.
Remember all of those radical
policies you proposed yesterday?
I kind of have to meet
with the nobles
who oppose them now,
and they're angry.
Huh? That took longer
than I thought.
I guess I'll go act like
a king for once, then.
Huh?
( scoffs )
This is outrageous!
You'll pay for this!
Don't think you can humiliate
the nobles and get away with it.
That's former nobles
from now on.
Preposterous.
Your titles, your land,
money, holdings,
all property
of the state now.
Well, given how quickly
I changed things up,
people were bound to throw
a hissy fit sooner or later.
Frankly, I'm surprised
that it took as long as it did.
I know you
didn't like them,
but you didn't have
to be so mean about it.
I'd worked so hard to keep them
under control peacefully.
Huh? Kept them
under control?
I used data from the
experiments we'd conducted
on the royal family's lands.
Then I distributed
the commercial rights
to all the noble factions
that backed my family.
Utilizing the success
we gained from doing that,
we were able to keep
the other major
political factions in check.
At the same time,
we could quietly break down
the smaller groups,
thus whittling away
our opponents' power base.
If you hadn't just
humiliated those guys,
we'd likely could have
had a bloodless victory
over the entire opposition!
Uh, what's wrong
with you two?
I didn't think
this was even possible,
but, Steph, you are actually
not a humongous idiot.
You mean you thought
I was stupid this whole time?
But that can't be right.
You are a Steph, aren't you?
Is it my imagination,
or did you just use my name
as a derogatory term?
Shut up, Steph,
you're just a Steph.
My God!
You two are terrible!
That is possibly the most
unfair insult in history!
In fact, I graduated
top of my class
at the most prestigious
academy in the country,
and I have connections
with every major family
through my former classmates.
She graduated
from high school already
and has lots of friends.
You know, she's like an entitled
rich little princess literally.
Shiro:
And she has big boobies, too.
Sora? Shiro?
We didn't decide did we,
what we were gonna make you do
for losing that game
of blackjack?
You're really gonna
get it now, Steph.
No mercy.
Wait! No!!
Th‐there are
t‐too many people here.
( gasps )
Ahh!
Sh‐Shiro, don't let go
of my hand no matter what!
You... you made me, Sora.
It was your idea
to come to town, Sora.
What's going on?
We got something
we need to do. Uh...
Wait, why is everyone
looking at us funny?
That's because...
you made me wear this crap!
Of course
they're going to stare!
Woof.
Couldn't you have come up
with a more dignified
demand than this?
Okay, Steph, now shake.
Oh, my God,
I can't disobey.
That's the rule, Steph.
In accordance
with the law of the pledges,
you are officially
our dog for the day.
( groans )
Now your outfit is weird...
but they seem more scared
than anything else.
I'll tell you why.
It's because the king
of Elkia is walking around
with someone dressed
as a Warbeast on a leash.
( gasps ) Wait!
You say you're dressed
like a Warbeast?
"Exceed rank number 14.
Their territory,
the Eastern Federation,
is one of the largest.
They possess superior senses
and physical abilities,
as well as a sixth sense
that allows them
to read people's minds!"
In other words,
the Eastern Federation
is an Eden composed entirely
of hot girls with animal ears!
No, there are men
and old people, too.
Okay! Time to conquer
the beasts of Paradise!
We're going after
the animal girls!
Ready, let's go!
Wait! They're one of the three
biggest countries
in the world!
Silence!
You and your false ears
shall not stand between me
and the joy of authentic
animal‐eared goddesses!
The Eden I've only dreamt of
awaits its true master!
Hmm?
Sora, before
you do that...
Oh, that's right.
Onward we go.
Lead the way.
Right.
Wait a sec.
( chokes )
I'm tied up?
Son of a bitch.
( sighs )
I can't believe we didn't find
a single thing anywhere.
This kingdom is weird.
I know, right?
This looks good,
but it tastes like dookie.
I think there's a shortage
of things like sugar,
salt, and butter.
Is that why Steph's
cookies were so good,
because they have better
ingredients at the castle?
Mm.
I finally found you!
Oh, hey, Steph.
Where you been?
What do you mean?
Uh, huh?
You left me tied to a lamppost
in the middle of town.
You're saying you just
conveniently forgot?
Sorry about that, Steph.
Now sit.
( pants )
You asked for forgiveness
and then you make me sit.
This is so wrong!
I can't take this anymore.
I've got to do something
about these two.
But if I'm going to stand
any chance
of beating them in a game,
it has to be a game
based on pure luck,
one where they can't calculate
their way into winning.
I've got it.
I demand one more match!
Now stand.
Hmm, okay, what do you want
from me now, Steph?
The same thing
you wanted this morning
that I didn't understand‐
The IRL.
Oh, Steph,
I knew you would‐ ( groans )
I will be happy to except
on behalf of Blank.
If you lose, you have
to do one thing I tell you to.
Sis, please,
my manhood needs this.
That's fine with me.
We'll compete to see
whether the next person
to go down that alley
is a man or a woman!
Best out of ten wins.
Aschente!
This doesn't
make sense!
Did you really think
it'd be random?
People usually have reasons
for going into town, you know.
Huh?
What Shiro did is assessed
the male‐to‐female ratio
by applying data
on time‐based variables‐
occupations, and employment
rate for this area
to the general trends that
we've observed in the past.
I rule.
Do you always take
this stuff so seriously?
But, of course, because
when it comes to games‐
Both:
We're always serious.
It's time to pay up, Steph.
I think I'll take
your underwear.
( sobs )
That's it isn't it?
I really am ruined
forever now, aren't I?
Hey, Shiro,
this is actually starting
to get really
depressing and sad.
I'm just 11 years old.
I'm a kid,
so I don't understand.
You seem like
you're in a bad mood.
might want to go easy
on Steph from now on.
Whatever.
I'll have you know,
I'm just getting started.
As far as my skills go,
you haven't seen anything yet.
On the contrary, I think
we've both seen plenty.
( gasps )
You'll regret that one!
Aschente!
( whimpers )
( wails )
( shudders )
( groans )
( laughs )
One‐ one more,
I want to play one more game!
You don't have much
left to lose.
( giggles )
A temporary defeat
is, uh, trivial
so long as it leads
to ultimate victory!
Hey, you know,
I'm starting to understand
why Elkia ended
up in such a bad state.
This time it'll be pure,
100% chance!
How many seconds until
those birds fly away?
( sighs )
Fine, I'll let you
bet first.
Aschente.
What's your bet?
Huh? A‐aschente.
Uh, let's see,
I bet 30 seconds.
Then I'll take...
three seconds!
Hey, that's against
the rules!
I don't believe you stated
any rules, right?
Steph, just give
it up, already.
Why?
Huh?
What did I ever do
to deserve this?
All I want
is to help people
for the sake of Elkia.
Why can't luck be on
my side even once?
Steph...
( sighs )
'Cause nothing's decided
by chance alone.
Huh?
Rules, statistics,
emotional states,
any number of invisible
factors can can combine
to produce an unpredictable
but inevitable result.
So the victor's decided
before the game even begins.
Luck isn't a thing.
For example,
what's the probability
of drawing the ace of spades
from a deck with no jokers?
Steph:
It's one in 52, isn't it?
Sora:
Normally, yes. But what
if it's a brand‐new deck?
The position of the cards
in a new deck
are typically identical.
So that means
If you take out the jokers
and draw the card
at the very bottom...
it's the ace of spades
almost 100% of the time.
Uh, hold on!
Oh, that's right,
I didn't say a word
about it being
a new deck, did I?
Rather... you didn't ask.
You see, being in the know
gives you the power
to turn the probability
of winning
from 1.92% to 100%.
The more knowledgeable party
will be the inevitable victor.
This is why the Imanity
keep losing over and over
and why we're at a loss
for what to do next.
Uh, explain.
We don't have
enough information.
Before we can invade
the animal‐girl kingdom
we have to know something
about them, anything,
though preferably
their weakness.
We've heard that they have
a sharp sixth sense
but that's not too much
to go off of.
Shiro:
They can read minds.
Sora:
If that's true,
then nothing we come up with
is gonna work against them.
It won't even
be a real game.
I've read every
book and paper
in the palace
and found nothing.
And there's not a
single bookstore or
library in this town.
Do these people even care?
Do they want to lose
forever?
Has he been looking
for information
about this world ever since
he was coronated?
You know what they say,
only an idiot starts
a fight he can't win.
True, but we have
to do something
or we'll never get anywhere!
Even if it means
sacrificing ourselves,
we have to keep
fighting for Elkia
before it's too late.
One more screw‐up,
and this kingdom is finished.
I know you're proud
of this country,
but it's still on
the verge of destruction.
Don't forget that.
Steph: All that time,
they weren't fooling
around after all.
Rather, they were
shouldering the fate
of 3 million
Imanity and I...
I didn't‐ I didn't
even realize it.
Sora: You know,
all things considered,
you really did a good job
of keeping things in check.
so far, Steph.
I was wondering why there
was so little resistance
to all those radical
reforms of ours.
You really had those
noblemen in line.
Shiro:
Good job being
smart, Steph.
Sora:
What you said
seriously helped us out.
So thanks for that.
Sora... Shiro?
Please, don't cry.
Let's all keep working
hard together, right?
Okay, Steph?
That's all I want.
That's all I want!
( howls and yelps )
That's nice,
but we're still
backed in a corner here,
and we don't have the key
to the one exit I can find.
What the?
It's dark already?
Shiro:
Wow!
Sora:
Awesome.
Both:
Laputa really exists.
Oh, that's the kingdom
of Avant Heim.
It's one of our
world's Phantasmas.
You mean, the
second‐ranked Exceed?
How the hell am I supposed
to play a game with that?
Sora, do you think‐
Yeah.
The best thing would be
for us to get one
of those Flugel up there
and bring them over to our side.
But how are we gonna get to 'em?
Both:
Ba *se
It's not falling.
I guess it's gonna take
more than magic words.
If you're looking
for a Flugel,
there's one that lives
near here.
Huh?
About five years ago,
it showed up at the doors
of the Elkia national library.
It defeated my grandfather
in a game
and won the library
and everything in it.
Funny, huh?
Oh, you had
a library, huh?
You bet your knowledge away?!
Are your heads full of shit?!
That's humanity's only weapon!
Steph, sit.
Down, girl.
( whimpers )
Stay.
No, please, wait!
People are staring at me!
Sora:
Exceed rank six,
the Flugel,
They were the soldiers
on the front lines,
created during the ancient
war to kill the gods.
I can't believe
there was one so close.
Wait, Sora,
are you two sure
you really want to challenge
a monster like that?
Sora: The only way we're
going to stand a chance
of saving this place
is if we can get a hold
of the knowledge
this god‐killer has.
Shiro:
You don't have to come
if you don't want to.
Steph:
Of course
I want to come.
Steph, from what I hear
the Flugel supposedly only
played one game, and that's it.
Is that really
the case?
Yes, according
to the records.
Perfect.
Well, looks like
this is it.
Time to start
conquering the world.
All:
Whoa...
Shiro:
Neato.
Now then, where's this cute
little angel of ours?
( whimpers )
( chuckles )
That's not the kind of angel
I was expecting.
That's an angel of death.
Excusez‐moi,
you wee little personas.
I'm afraid mi library
is no sus library.
( all groan )
Both:
Whoa...
That ruined it.
( giggles )
Flugel:
Woe is to Steph.
Death should not
have taken thee so young.