What the heck is going on here?
Huh, what? this?
Well, in case you didn't catch on, we're
siblings, so don't get the wrong idea.
Oh, rejected by my own brother.
I don't care about your stupid relationship!
I'm asking you why you didn't call that girl out
if you knew she was totally trying to cheat me back there!
Now I've blown my chance at ruling the kingdom!
Pledge eight states.
"Being caught cheating during a game
is grounds for an instant loss," right?
Yeah, duh! And now thanks to you,
some nobody is gonna take over my kingdom.
My life is over!
So, basically.
She lost her match to the cheater, and she's a sore loser.
She fell for it.
Let me get this straight.
You got totally hustled,
lost all your worldly possessions,
and somehow that's supposed to be our fault?
Ha, whatever, toots.
What was that?!
Not only that, when you get called out on it,
you completely flip out and
start yapping like a little dog.
Pull it together.
You're an emotional time bomb,
too unstable to think logically
and too scared to take any risks.
Let me ask you, does crazy run in your family?
Or are you just a natural loser?
Hmm...
You take that back, right... now.
Huh?
Say what you want about me,
but I will not tolerate such
insults against my grandfather!
You take that back this instant!
Well, I'm right about that explosive temper,
a foolish king and a foolish granddaughter.
I said that's enough!
Then how about a game?
A game?
Yeah, aren't all conflicts
supposed to be resolved through games?
That's like this world's second rule, right?
So how's a game of rock‐paper‐scissors sound?
You want to play that?
Yeah, but one thing.
It's simple.
I'll only play paper.
So I can only win this game if I play paper.
But say I beat you at rock or scissors,
you'll lose, too, so it ends up being a tie.
Then what happens if we both play the same thing?
In that case, it still ends up being a tie,
but if you can play anything besides paper,
you can actually win. Easy enough for you?
Oh, I get it.
So that's the trick.
I'm in. So what are we betting?
How about if you win,
whatever you wish will be my command.
I'll tell you how you were cheated,
and if you're still mad about me
dissing your stupid old grandfather so much
you can have us put to death.
Do what?!
But if I win the game,
you'll be on my leash, of course.
It's a high stakes game or
rock‐paper‐scissors with my life on the line.
Fair enough for you?
And if we tie?
Then I'll just give you a hint about our cheating methods.
in exchange, you can do me a tiny favor.
I'm getting worried 'cause when this gold runs out,
we're more or less gonna be hobos on this planet.
So you're saying you want me to give you a place to stay.
Mmm...
Fine.
Then challenge excepted.
I swear by the pledges.
Aschente! Aschente it is!
Ha! I'm not gonna fall for his trap that easily.
He might be trying to convince me
that his rules give me the advantage,
but there's still a one‐in‐three
chance that the game ends in a draw.
Basically, he's shooting for a
tie, so he wins a place to stay.
Sorry to disappoint you, smarty
pants, but victory won't come that easy.
Even with these rules if I just play rock
I have a two‐in‐three chance of winning.
Same as scissors, also a two‐in‐three chance.
But with paper, I only have a one‐in‐three chance to win,
So my best chance is throwing scissors or rock.
But since he said he'd only play paper,
that makes it more risky on my end to play rock,
which is the only way he can win.
In other words, he's trying to force me to play scissors.
Ha! So much for your genius ploy.
Did you really think I was stupid enough to fall for that?
I'll crush your plans and play rock!
No, wait a minute!
Let's think about this, Stephanie Dola.
There's a two‐in‐three chance I'll win if I play rock,
but there's also a one‐in‐three chance I'll lose.
So, wait a minute.
Unless he's totally lying, he said he'd only play paper.
So if he does, then he'll risk
a one‐in‐three chance of losing
as well as a one‐in‐three chance of winning.
But if he doesn't, he'll have a two‐in‐three
chance of losing and absolutely no chance of winning.
Since that's the case, there shouldn't be
any reason for him to play anything else.
It's obvious. He's got to pick... paper.
Ready? Here we go.
Yeah, I'm ready.
One, two... But I hope
Shoot!
I'll admit, good try.
But not good enough.
You probably thought I was gonna
try to goad you into playing rock,
but once you saw my expression
you realized I couldn't win
unless I played anything but paper.
I'll give you that much.
You did actually end up blocking me from winning.
But still, your best bet would have been paper.
Yeah, but with scissors, I could double
my chances to win compared to paper.
Of course, that's how I knew
you'd end up picking scissors.
You were so busy trying to get inside my
head, you didn't think that I was in yours.
Otherwise, you would have wised
up and played paper for the win.
See, I told you‐ you're just not good enough.
Oh, don't be so hard on yourself,
the results were pretty much a given.
Sorry, but you had no chance.
Fine, I get it.
You were trying to corner me into a tie.
I'll find you housing.
No, that's all right.
Hey, Sis, what did I say my prize would be?
If you won, she'd owe you a tiny favor.
And I said that favor was?
Didn't say.
Oh, w‐wait a minute! That's not true!
I know I asked if you wanted a
place to stay before we started
Yep, but do you remember my response?
Uh...
No...
That's right. Those were my words, not his.
He just complained about money.
I guess you didn't notice, but this game's big catch
was that whether you lost or tied,
the risk was gonna be the same.
No fair! That's cheating!
Hey, I stuck to the rules of the
pledges when I laid the game out for you.
Why should I take blame if you didn't get it?
So since I'm sure you're wondering...
why don't I tell you the favor?
I want you...
...to love me!
Huh?
To love me!
What do you think, Sis? Your
brother came up with the perfect plan!
Pledge number six‐ any bets made in
accordance with the pledges must be upheld.
All I have to do is make her fall in love with
me and we'd be in her palace and rolling in riches.
Uh, you could have had all of that if
you'd just said, "give me all of your stuff."
Say what?
Sora...
you succumbed to your desires.
I did what?
You mean after all the genius work I've put into my plan,
I was thwarted by my not‐so‐subconscious
fear of being a virgin the rest of my life?!
Even when faced against my mighty brain,
you're telling me, Little Sora, down in my pants...
But you said you never wanted a girlfriend.
Remember, you said all you needed was me.
Shiro...
I was just trying to look cool
when I said that. It was a lie!
It's not like I can date my sister.
You're only 11, anyway. I'm a healthy and virile young man
and a man's got sexual needs and sexual needs
and sexual needs.
Did I mention sexual needs?
Yeah, you said it four times already.
I know the ten pledges are set in stone,
but... am I really jealous that he's
gushing over his sister and ignoring me?
I mean, we just met.
No! It's nonsense.
I'll never love you!
Baby.
No way! There's no way I'm feeling this.
Falling in love is just some chemical imbalance, right?
It's just an illusion.
Come on, stay strong.
Fight it!
Fight the urges!
Hey, mind if I call you Steph, from now on?
That would be wonderful!
No, no, no, no, no, this isn't
right! What the hell is wrong with me?!
Uh, hey, Steph?
Uh‐huh?
Are you good with us staying in the palace?
But, of course!
Wow, those pledges really have a
hold on these people, don't they?
Sora?
Yo!
You're losing your virginity.
Congrats.
Uh...
My cute body isn't ready for defiling.
...is happening in front of you!
Why? I'm cool with it.
Well, as your brother, I'm not!
One's, youth should be wholesome and healthy.
Why don't you see how healthy she is?
Accidental boob grab.
Nice move.
It was an accident!
So soft, voluptuous.
He's touching me!
And now the moment we've all been waiting for...
The pantaloons.
Please, you have to...
get off me!
Oh, Sora! I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. I swear, I'm really
sorry. I'll never touch boobs again.
I promise I'll never touch any
girl again. Please forgive me,
I just thought this might be the only chance in
my life to ever lay hands on any boobies anywhere.
I mean, hentai games and oppai mousepads...
Did he get brain damaged or wh‐
Sora, where are you? Please don't leave me here.
I don't want to be alone. I'm scared.
Where did you go? You can't
abandon me in this scary place.
Please, Sora, where are you?
You've got to be kidding me.
This is what happens when you
two are apart from each other?
A couple of weirdos.
Sora!
Shiro!
Hug!
Okay, I'm done. You two are freaks.
So you're like aliens or something?
Yep.
Then that's why you're trying
You don't think it's weird
that we came from another planet?
I know there's magic and sorcery and other
stuff like that, so anything's possible, really.
This really is a fantasy world.
But I guess my real question is,
is this how your people normally take baths?
Well, Shiro's not a huge fan of baths.
She hates taking them 'cause she says
the Pedo Police will take me away for watching her.
That's why we invited our good old friend
Mr. Steam to help out.
No pervs allowed, Sora.
If you know it makes her uncomfortable,
then why don't you just wait outside?
Obviously, we can't be too far apart from each other.
So Mr. Steam comes in very handy.
But don't despair, Steph,
I'll be sure to check out your boobage.
Oopsie!
Heya, Steph, my hand's all slippery!
Mind picking that up for me?
Uh... what is it?
Oh, it's just a secret tool from another world.
A secret tool?
Oh!
As long as Steph grabs the phone first, I
can check out her naughty nudey nakedness
without Shiro getting in the shot!
What's going on?
Did you grab it?
Yeah...
Perfect view, too. Pew pew.
It's hard to move in, and it's so frilly.
I used to wear that all the
time back when I was a little kid.
Perfect fit, huh?
It's a bit formal for my taste, but it's kind
of like cosplay, so I guess that's cool, right?
My butler fantasy!
You look exquisite, Steph, ravishing.
Oh, you.
Huh?!
Don't be such an idiot!
What the heck is her problem, anyway?
Maybe herself?
I'll be right back. Better go make some tea!
That was really weird.
Sora, you really don't get girls, do you?
Um, Miss, wait.
Hold on, Miss. Perhaps, you should let us make the tea?
Don't worry about me!
Um, Ma'am, why are you dressed like a hobo?
Maybe she's sick. Call a doctor!
Simply delicious. You're quite
the cook, aren't you, sweet cheeks?
Sora, you should totally marry her.
Huh, your wife?!
Oh, my, I'm embarrassed!
Miss Dola no!
Please stop!
Okay, keep your wits about you, Stephanie Dola.
You can't let him undo you with his unworldly wiles.
I'm sorry if I kept you waiting.
What the?
Sora?
Uh...
You'd never guess there's a tournament to
find the next king by the looks of this place.
It's like a ghost town.
Hm?
So what the hell language is that?
Not sure.
It's a real Imanity.
There used to be a time when Elkia was
the largest of all the Imanity nations.
And what's Imanity?
That's the human race.
Oh, so, us?
Imanity once had many nations,
and they were spread all throughout the world,
But many of them are already dying out
by the time my grandfather took power.
Now there is only Elkia.
It's gotten to the point where we have to gamble our
territories in hopes of gaining even just a little ground.
Then who else is there to play against,
something other than humans or Imanity or whatever?
Yes, exactly.
So other aliens like us, or what?
Well, let's see.
There are a total of 16 sentient races
that must abide by God's ten sacred pledges.
Collectively, we just refer to all the
races as The Exceed to keep it simple.
The first order is the Old Deus
who were defeated by the One God.
The Phantasma are the second order
and The Elementals are the third.
Skipping to the seventh order, we
have the Elves, who are great at magic
and comprise the world's largest nation.
On the lower end, we have the Warbeasts at number 14,
and The Sirens at the 15th...
Hold on a second.
What's up with the all this order business?
It's like a ranking system.
From what I've been told,
it's determined by a race's affinity for magic.
And what about Imanity?
Well, we're at 16.
Dead last, huh?
That's just the way it is.
We have zero magical abilities.
Zero? So Imanity can't use magic?
Right, unlike the other races,
Imanity lacks the Spirit Circuits that would
allow us to connect to the source of all magic.
And what's worse than that,
we can't even tell if someone else is using magic or not.
So you think you can't win.
Well, you know what they call that, don't you?
A self‐fulfilling prophecy.
Huh?
Hey, Steph, any libraries around here?
Uh, well, there's a bunch of books in the study.
However...
They're all in Imanity.
We'll just have to learn it then, won't we?
Yeah, I guess so.
Sora?
Huh?
I learned it.
That was fast.
Praise me more.
Yeah, way to go, Little Sis.
She learned it?
You make me so proud of you, you tiny little genius.
She's gotta be joking, right?
She really learned the entire language that fast?
Yeah, so what?
But that's impossible.
It's only been like five minutes.
Since your spoken language is the same as ours, it's easy.
Catch up, Sora.
Huh, a man should take his
time, instead of finishing quickly.
This... is totally insane.
My, how very small of you, Brother.
No weiner jokes!
His rock‐paper‐scissors scheming,
her genius level intelligence, solid teamwork,
complete trust and confidence...
You think you're so special...
then it's possible that these two...
...that these two could be the ones to save Elkia!
And the victor of this match is Kurami Zell!
Steph, what made you want to rule Elkia?
Huh?
I stayed up all night reading all these books.
I've learned a lot about this kingdom
and your grandfather and his whole story.
Oh.
Were you scared of losing your status in the royal family?
No, not really.
Then it was Elkia you wanted to save.
That's pretty much it.
Of course I have other reasons.
In any case, my grandfather was
forced to gamble our country's territory,
but he kept losing.
Hence his title, "The Foolish King."
But despite people resenting him, my
grandfather believed in the potential of Imanity.
He didn't care we were the lowest
ranked or that we can't use magic,
He believed that if we tried
hard enough, we could win somehow.
I want to show the world that my
grandfather wasn't just some old fool.
If I can become king, then I can take our territory back.
Then I can prove to everyone
that my grandfather was right,
that we can win.
Tell me, Steph, do you love this country,
this world?
Yeah...
with all of my heart.
Wow, nice.
I'm kind of jealous you can say that with such conviction,
but... there's no way that wish is coming true.
In fact, as it stands,
this country is already doomed.
Once the next king takes the throne,
it's all over.
Uh, Kurami?
So it's time for the coronation already, huh?
Well, well, Princess,
don't tell me you've been dressing
in bed sheets ever since I beat you.
I believe I heard you say this was the dress that
your beloved grandfather gave you before he died.
Here, I don't need it.
Oops.
Just face it, you lost, so move on.
It would be wise if you didn't make the same mistakes
as the fool who gave you that dress.
You know, if you keep acting like
that you're only gonna prove her right.
In case you hadn't noticed, the game's already started.
Sora?
I'm sure you know pledge six‐
all bets made in accordance
with the pledges must be upheld.
So this dress is yours.
But just for a while, okay?
Looks like the granddaughter of The Foolish King
has inherited some fools for servants, too.
Hey, Shiro?
Mm?
You're gonna stick by your bro no matter what happens?
Mm.
Just like I promised, I'll follow you anywhere.
That's a good answer!
This is a pretty miserable situation, so‐
Liar, you know you're loving this.
Well, it sure beats sitting at home and now you
can't say I don't take you anywhere fun, right?
Hey, Steph, you just gonna sit there forever?
Come on, you want to win that
dress back from her, don't you?
Let's get going. Hurry.
Uh...
You ready?
But where?
We're going to prove that your
grandfather wasn't the fool people thought.
Huh? Sora!
What's going on?
I'm not just having another fantasy, am I?
Oh, I almost forgot. Thanks, Steph.
Those cookies were great, nice work.
Yum!
I'm so glad you liked them!
What's next?
I don't know.
Being king might be fun.
You still like your sheet dress, Steph?
I never liked it!