I could not hate baths any more.
Hey, Shiro, how am I supposed
to wash you if you keep squirming?
Come on, sis, after all the
craziness that went down today,
I'd say a bath is definitely in order.
Just go with it.
I hate taking baths 'cause it makes my hair stiff.
If that's the case, why don't you try some of my shampoo?
W‐where'd the hell'd you come from, Jibril?!
Suffering from tired, dried‐out hair?
Get soft, silky, flowing tresses with
Flugel's very own Spirit Water Blend.
And as a bonus, I, Jibril, your new slave, will
even throw in a free back scrubbing for my Masters.
Let me explore those hot alien bodies.
Shiro, watch out!
Her very existence is 18 and over!
Jibril, wait.
Oh!
You just sit there and watch, naughty girl.
What? That's not fair.
The stupid steam's covering up all the good stuff.
Look at that, already bossing her around like a pro.
You've really made your big brother proud,
learning to crack the whip at such a young age.
I really hate the fact that I'm
starting to get used to this crap.
Uh, what in the world is this?
I prepared it for my Masters.
I do believe in your country they call a kitchen.
Um, excuse me, Steve.
It's Steph!
My name is Stephanie Dola.
Well, "Dola" is ugly, and I
don't care for you much anyway,
so I'm going to call you something
easier to remember like Dolly.
UGH! Dolly?!
By the way, I received a message from Sora.
"Looks like there's plenty of sugar and butter
here, so feel free to bake whatever you want."
Message ends.
Really?
Oh, think of all the desserts I can make with this.
Ohh! Hold on, that's just their backhanded
way of getting me to bake goodies for them.
Why do they always try to take
advantage of poor little me?
But if it weren't for you, we would have lost.
Thanks a lot, Steph.
I'm on it!
So this is how the lowly Imanity experience
that strange feeling called love, isn't it?
Huh? Love?
No, no, no, you're wrong!
I believe you were ordered to fall in love,
not stay in love... so what's the deal, Dolly?
Why do you still seem to be so affected by it, hmm?
At first, I thought you were useless,
but your clownish behavior is actually quite amusing.
Greetings, Kurami, I'm finally back.
You wanted some information, right?
Or was it food? Wait, I know.
How about me?
Thanks, but I'll take my clothes first.
Mm, this is great.
We had that poor girl you beat in the tournament to thank.
Ever since she started enacting the new King's policies,
the quality of life in Elkia
has really started to improve.
Whatever. Little Princess. Hmph.
She's just the puppet of a puppet, and as
shameless as her grandfather was foolish.
I know you feel guilty for trying
to cheat her out of the kingdom,
and I know you've been working on an
apology when you didn't think I was watching.
You're so adorable, Kurami.
Hey, how'd you, I mean, more importantly,
don't you have any intel to report?
Oh, well, this and that.
It seems that the new King has somehow
acquired a Flugel as a personal slave
and he's really interested in the Eastern Federation.
I think that's about it.
All of that's true?
Okay, maybe I got a little carried away,
but remember, it's for the sake of Imanity.
It definitely has nothing to do with being in love.
Now then, dear Jibril,
tell me what you know about the Eastern Federation,
the sexy animal‐girl paradise we're about to conquer.
Well, I guess this country's pretty much done for.
As you wish, my King.
The various Warbeast clans were
embroiled in the civil war for many years,
mostly due to physical differences,
but the shrine priestess put an end to
the battles in less than half a century.
The clans unified into a massive naval empire
and became the world's third‐largest
country, the Eastern Federation.
So, a land of cat girls, dog girls, fox girls,
rabbit girls, and all other kinds of animal girls,
and they'll all be mine.
All right, we must conquer them at once.
But to do that, we'll need to utilize all that precious
knowledge you've been collecting over the last millennia.
I am sorry, master, I doubt that would do much good.
Unfortunately, I can think of no path to victory
when it comes to facing the Eastern Federation.
Jibril, you don't mean that.
You're saying Blank can't win?
Not quite.
What I mean is I won't be of
much help in forming your strategy.
There was once a time where I, too,
fought the Eastern Federation... and lost.
That settles it.
I knew Elkia had another nation's support.
It must be the Warbeasts.
Okay, then, so what you think is going on?
You of all people should know.
On at least four occasions, Elven Gard challenged
the Eastern Federation, and lost each time.
Hmm... we might have won if the players
weren't those senile elders, but okay.
The point is, when I faced Blank, I lost,
and that means they were able
to overcome your Elven magic,
and that Flugel was next.
In other words, they must be
using some sort of Warbeast sorcery
that even an Elf couldn't detect.
Are you sure?
That's gotta be it.
There's no way Imanity could beat a higher race by itself.
Don't underestimate humanity.
He's got some nerve.
So you and the Elves both got your asses handed to you?
What the hell kind of game did you play anyway?
When setting the rules,
one of the Federation's conditions is that
the loser has their memories of the game erased.
Now do you understand what I mean?
Yeah, I get it, it's impossible.
What you mean it's impossible?
If they wipe your memories when you lose
and you have no recollection of the game,
how are you gonna adapt your strategy
the next time you challenge them?
To top it off, they can also read your mind?
How are we supposed to beat a race like that?
Don't be such a Steph, Steph.
It's pretty obvious.
Huh? No, wait a second.
It doesn't add up.
What doesn't?
Since trying to beat the Warbeasts is so pointless,
their enemies should eventually stop trying, right?
It would be less painful that way for everyone.
That, dear sis, is why you suck at strategy games
despite being a little smarter than me.
They've got some kind of slam‐dunk
method of beating Flugel and even Elves.
Why don't they pretend like they're vulnerable instead?
Then they'd lure the enemy in, give them a
healthy beat down, and snatch their land easy.
That play style is just... mean.
Appalled!
There is something weird about it, though.
How could they have expanded their
country so much in just half a century?
See? I told you it's strange!
Master, wait, I just thought of something.
I think I might be able to explain how that happened.
Oh, really now? Let's hear it.
I saw something in here somewhere.
Only one country has challenged the Eastern Federation
in the last ten years.
Only one? Who's dumb enough to do that?
Why don't I just show you? It'll be faster.
Come along, Dolly, you're going with us.
All right then, masters.
Hold on tight and don't let go.
Now then, if everyone is ready.
Wha‐what's going on?!
Wow, it's so nice and clear today.
J‐Jibril, what the heck did you just do?!
Ever hear of teleporting?
Right, I keep forgetting.
I'm living in a fantasy world now.
So how far can you teleport?
I can travel as far as I can see
and to any location I've visited before.
So a zoom spell.
How was poor little Imanity able to survive in a war
against a whole race full of monsters like her?
That's been the most perplexing
mystery in all our history.
Oh, I remember it like it was just yesterday.
The Dragonia, Giganto, and Old Deus all storming
the battlefield, 50 Flugel desperately fighting
to sever a single Dragon's head,
and then 200 of our finest facing a god in vain!
Why, I can almost smell the blood.
Ah, yes, the good old days.
Have a look over there, master.
What I'm looking at here?
Some ugly high‐rise crapping up the fantasy landscape?
It's huge.
Oh, that's the Eastern Federation's Elkian embassy.
Well, that kind of seems like overkill, do you think?
Actually, that used to be the Elkian palace,
but the Eastern Federation did a bit of remodeling.
Ah! Hey, hold on!
So that place used to be your palace? Why do they have it?
All starting to make sense now, Master?
In the last ten years, only one
country has challenged the Federation.
Uh‐huh, and blew it, too.
Yeah. The challenger was Elkia.
You hanging in there, Sora?
Yeah, sorry, just wallowing in despair, that's all.
UWAH!
Even the Elves gave up after four losses,
but Elkia challenged these guys eight times
and bet half its kingdom?
I'm starting to think that old King really was an idiot.
Hey, what was that? Weren't you the one that kept claiming
that he was right despite what everyone else said?
And thanks to his recklessness,
your territory got cut in half.
You expect me to defend that?
Can you just imagine all the industry and farming
we could have if the country still had all that land?
Man, he was as hopeless as you are.
Did he just suck at getting lucky thinking if he
kept trying that eventually he might somehow win?
Okay, maybe it's true that my
grandfather wasn't good at games,
but he wasn't stupid enough to risk the three
million lives under his care unless he had a good reason.
The people came first!
Unlike the two of you, he was kind
and loving and reasonable at least.
Well, excuse me for being cruel and awful.
Heh. Besides, if throwing away half your shit qualifies
you as reasonable, that I'm happier being a jerk.
Eh, Maybe you're right and he was a good king,
But just a good king for a bunch of whiners
that won't take things into their own hands.
That's more likely.
Useless friggin' humans,
completely hopeless, every last one of them.
Huh?
You can go ahead and mock me, I don't care.
But don't insult my grandfather or what he believed in.
Hey, Steph, wait, come back!
Too far, way too far.
After finding out about this ridiculous state of affairs,
how else should I react?
Hmm?
They're yummy.
Damn.
They are good.
Um, Granddaddy, what's this key for?
Well, sweetie, it opens the lock to
something I've stored away that's very important.
Oooh! I've heard about that!
So it's for your secret man books
that you can't show to other people?
No, no, my dear, that's something else.
I mean.
This key, this is a key of hope.
Hope, huh?
Maybe someday, it will belong to you.
What do I do with it, Granddaddy?
I want you to find someone very special to give it to,
someone to whom you can entrust our kingdom,
someone who can carry the weight of Imanity's future.
Like hell I'm ever giving this to that stupid‐
Hey, there, you got a second?
What the heck are you doing here?!
Dolly, I highly recommend you
return to the library immediately.
What's going on now?
Though I came here on my own,
I feel your presence would benefit my Master.
However, I won't force you.
Huh?
This is so ridiculous. Like they even care about me.
Fine! I'll go!
Master, no matter how hard you look, I doubt you'll
find evidence to justify the King's foolish actions.
No, that's not what I'm looking for.
Something about this is bugging me, though.
You wouldn't happen to be looking for
clues to help Dolly feel better, now would you?
Look, I'm just reviewing all the info so I don't make
the same mistake on my animal‐girl‐kingdom conquest.
So anyway, why'd the former king
challenge the Federation eight times?
A reasonable man responsible for three million
people wouldn't just rush into defeat again and again.
Right here, isn't this the first
place he offered up as a wager?
That's an omatite mine, isn't it?
Even though it's a valuable metal, Imanity
doesn't have the technology to refine it,
so it's worthless to us.
Then here's the second bet, then the third
bet, the fourth bet, and finally the eighth, here.
Up till the very last game when he bet the castle,
looks like he didn't wager anything of value.
Come on, I know we had a reason for it, but why?
Master?
Why wipe challengers' memories
when it only discourages them?
Why did Elven Gard challenge them four times?
Why did the former king...
no, wait.
Maybe he stopped at eight 'cause maybe by the eighth time,
he actually achieved his goal.
There is no written proof, but what if the last King
didn't lose his memories after all?
Master, please don't take this as being rude,
but from what I've seen, not all Imanity act
with the same forethought and attention as you.
Not all, but I'm sure some of them do,
and most of the time, they're probably misunderstood.
Now is the new King, it's my
duty to try and understand them.
I know what you're thinking, how can I possibly believe
that an inferior race like humanity actually has a chance?
No, I wasn't thinking that at all.
The answer's simple, really.
If you want to know the truth,
I don't believe in humanity.
Humans are lowly and stupid creatures,
every single last one of them, including me.
They're all crap.
It doesn't matter what planet they're from,
this one or my old one.
Not a damn thing's changed a bit.
I...
I've heard enough.
However, I believe in humanity's potential.
If you need proof, it's right here.
This little human is the real deal.
She's a shining example of our potential, our strength,
our hope, and our dreams that reach even beyond the gods.
I remember the first day we met.
It was almost eight years ago.
Back then, she was only three.
The first time she heard my
name, guess what her response was.
You seem so empty.
First off, she knew that my name meant sky,
and then she noticed that I was smiling
just 'cause everyone else in the room was.
A double entendre at three years old.
I was so pumped. This was it.
I found someone who was worth something.
Also...
I wanted to be like her or at least try.
You know, back in our old world,
humans can fly through the sky
and even travel amongst the stars.
Sorry, but that's kind of hard to believe.
Yeah, no kidding, even humanity
itself doubted any of that was possible,
but someone eventually pulled it
off, the real deal, pulled it off.
That's why it's up to us to ensure
that the potential of the misunderstood
gets realized before it all goes to waste.
And that's the reason why I
need to start believing in him.
The former king was right.
Sora...
Huh?
I have something that I...
want to give you.
There's no doubt.
It's his porn.
I knew it!
But my dear Master, which door do you think it goes to?
People usually stash their porn in their own room.
So then, it's this one.
Actually, sis and I found it a long time ago.
Peace.
Huh?
Remember when I said this bed
was lopsided and hard to sleep on?
That was just the start of the puzzle.
With a little messing around here and there...
Ah, there you go, one secret room coming right up.
I give up. I don't know anything.
Hmm.
I leave this in hopes that you will
not be Imanity's last king but rather
the one who restores it.
I admit, I am not a wise king.
In fact, I fully expect to be
remembered as one of the most foolish.
But that is of no matter.
I take up this pen for the future King,
the one who will one day bring us to glory.
All I can do is trust that the story of my
pathetic and seemingly hopeless struggles...
Will someday assist you in your quest as our next king.
I knew it.
The old king didn't have his memories erased after all.
Unlike the Elves, the Warbeasts knew
Imanity didn't stand a chance to win
and looked down on them as easy prey.
They didn't erase his memories
because they wanted him to keep trying.
Was that some way to lure him in?
They purposefully went easy on him to make
him think he could beat them the next time.
But still, the king knew that, and he challenged
them anyway hoping to figure out how their game worked.
He deliberately gave them useless land
that he'd eventually try to take back.
So then if he played so many times, why didn't
he reveal the secrets of the game to anyone?
They probably made him take a pledge,
like he couldn't tell people as long as he lived.
So it was all for nothing?
Not quite.
Once he died, the pledge no longer applied.
He bet eight times,
but then he found a loophole in the pledges,
then entrusted that information to the next king.
Humanity's greatest gambler.
That's why he set up a gambling tournament to
find the next ruler, even if it ousted Steph.
Your former King, he made a bet.
He bet that a human, someone from the lowest‐ranked race,
would rise up and crush all the other races.
The possibility rests ever so close to naught.
However... it still remains.
Steph...
He just pretended to be a fool,
lost the bets but kept trying.
In reality, he was a great man
trying to save Imanity up until his death.
This is his trust in our people.
You know what, Steph? Your old Gramps‐
no, sorry, I mean the former king...
he really was a great man after all.
Granddaddy!
Well, it sure is one hell of a task he threw at us.
Don't worry, Sora, you and I can do it.
See, Jibril? Not all humans are so bad.
What do you think?
You ready for this?
Yes, ready indeed, Master.
Eastern Federation, your head's gonna
look mighty nice on the end of this pike.