Kurami:
What is this?
What have you done to him?
Sora:
King, oh, foolish King,
to be so cruel
as to give your servant
the order to slay his own queen?
Sora:
And now you tremble with rage
with not a word or explanation
to your loyal followers?
My Queen...
I cannot ask you...
or the knights
who lowered their swords
out of love for you
to take their weapons
and wield them against
their comrades.
But it is now clear‐
your beloved King
has been struck by madness!
I believe
that you are the only one
who can lead your people now.
Alas, the King is mad!
He must be brought to justice!
My Queen, the decision
is in your hands.
Excellent choice, my Queen,
my brave, honorable Queen!
You and your righteous warriors
saw the truth
through the enemy's
nefarious illusions.
Now rise against your oppressor
and usher in peace!
Stephanie:
Wait a minute, is this...
Shiro:
A revolt.
The appearance of a
third force, rebellion.
Then Sora planned all this?
( chuckles )
I told you...
I'd win without having to fight.
( theme song plays )
Stephanie:
Win without having to fight?
King:
Yes, of course.
The one who inherits
the throne must have
a special sort of wisdom,
my dear Stephanie.
I believe it will take
a creative approach
to save Elkia
from its current plight.
Yeah, but‐
King:
As you know,
we Imanity are
the weakest race in Disboard.
And that's why we must find
our own unique way
of facing those
who are stronger than us.
We must be clever.
Well, that's what
your grandpa thinks anyway.
I understand.
King:
Surely there's
someone out there
with the wisdom
to save Elkia,
Some brave soul who knows
how to turn
their weakness into strength.
Steph:
Could it be?
Sora:
Hear me out.
We do not seek bloodshed.
We seek what
all men seek‐
peace and the right
to live our lives freely.
All forces assist
the Red Queen's men now.
Shiro:
Good, surround them.
Don't let a single man fall.
Why, you spineless traitors.
Stephanie:
The red pieces
are protecting them.
Yep, To the black pieces,
it's like a protest.
Sora:
Will they be able to kill
their former comrades?
Kurami:
I can't believe this.
They beat my Elf magic?
What race could possibly
be helping the cheat?
There's no way I can let
someone like him
take over this country.
Hey, Crazy King Lady,
didn't you know?
You still have
some options here.
In real war, the battle
doesn't always have to end
with the king being killed,
but you know you're not
coming out on top.
Sora:
Surrender.
Oh...
Stephanie:
This is how you win
without fighting.
Sora.
Kurami:
( laughing )
Surrender?
( laughs )
I won't let you get away
with this.
I earned this country.
And it will belong to me.
All forces, sacrifice your lives
to slay the enemy king!
Go forth and destroy
every last traitor.
March!
Sora, we backed her
too far into a corner.
Shiro:
She's lost it.
Sora:
Yeah. I know.
Stephanie:
This is worse than before.
There's no such thing as
a peaceful solution after all.
Sora:
That's why I did it.
Huh?
( gasps )
Sora...
Sora:
Oppression, rule by fear,
dictatorships.
People never learn.
Sora:
Throughout history,
for whatever reason,
the lives of tyrants always
seem to end the same way‐
assassination at the hands
of someone close to them.
It happens without fail.
Sorry about that.
I guess our world just isn't
as friendly as yours is.
When it comes to war
and murder,
I'm afraid we have way more
experience than you do.
Man:
And the victory goes
to the challenger, Team Blank!
King:
Your dear old grandpa believes
with all his heart
that someone will rise
to the challenge,
someone who understands
true strength
through their limitations
and knows how to use
the strengths of others
to their advantage.
This person will
come to be the hope
and the potential
of Imanity.
Potential?
( laughs )
Oh, I knew that dress
would suit you, my dear.
( giggles )
So did I pull it off?
Uh‐‐
I mean, this is
the kind of strategy
your grandpa believed in,
isn't it?
More or less.
I think the old man
was onto something,
so I hope I did him justice.
And now no one will call him
a fool, I hope.
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
This means everything to me.
Sora, Shiro...
( crying )
There, there, Steph.
What kind of trick
did you use?
Trick?
Don't play dumb.
You may be clever,
but there's no way that Imanity
could beat Elf magic unaided.
Why, thank you,
I am quite clever, aren't I?
You should be glad.
Huh?
To be perfectly honest,
I didn't think that your idea
of getting the Elves to rule
alongside Imanity
Then why did you‐
was such a bad one, really.
Because your attitude
towards Imanity is crap.
Doesn't the idea that
we can't survive without
Elves' protection seem a bit
self‐deprecating to you?
Hold on‐
You can't see that the Imanity
have their own way
of doing things.
That's why you lost.
You were so stuck up on
the idea that we had
some imaginary spell going on,
that you couldn't see
our merits for what they were.
Stop saying things like that.
Humans can't defeat magic.
It's just not possible.
Sora:
If that's what you think,
that's fine.
I guess you just can't see
your own potential.
But listen‐
it doesn't matter
whether we're up against
elves or gods.
Blank never loses a fight.
You got that?
Don't underestimate humanity.
Huh?
( sobbing )
Whoa! Aw, shit.
Do you have any idea how much
trouble I went through
to get the elves
to help me, do you?!
Wait, uh, look‐
It was really,
really tough!
( sobs )
I didn't underestimate anyone!
I was serious!
Sora, look what you did.
This is my fault?!
You made her cry.
Shiro:
Look, I know you're still a
virgin and all,
but can't you even
talk to girls?
Sora:
What?! Come on!
( chuckles )
Man:
Now, this gentleman standing
before us, Sora,
is the new winner
of the tournament for the crown.
Before I go on, is there anyone
to challenge him?
Very well, then in accordance
with the final wish
of our former king,
I crown Sora the new
King of Elkia!
Sora:
Hold it!
Man:
What the‐ this again?
It's not Sora.
It's Blank.
The both of us are Blank
together, you see?
So you got two Kings.
Man:
Unfortunately,
I'm afraid that won't do.
The 10 pledges
require us to specify
a designated representative,
a single representative.
Then we'll split it up,
I guess.
I'll be the king in name only‐
Shiro:
Objection! If you become king
by yourself,
then you're gonna
make a harem.
You won't need
me anymore.
Sora:
A harem?
What are they even
talking about?
If it's going to be name only,
I will be the king.
It's all same, isn't it?
All right then, fine,
I'll start over‐
Sora:
Objection!
Now, now, wait a second,
Dear Sister.
It's rare for you to make
a joke like that.
Are pigs about to fly?
Watch out.
I mean it.
Very well then,
I guess we'll just have to
play a game, won't we?
Both:
Better prepare yourself,
'cause there's no way
I'll lose.
( weakly )
Just one more round.
Okay...
Admit defeat already,
would you?
You're the big dummy
who said two wins in a row.
What's wrong
with there being
more than one king
anyway, huh?
Shiro:
Sora, hold on and take a look
at this, pledge number seven.
"Conflicts between groups
will be conducted
by an appointed representative
with absolute authority."
We were both representatives,
so we both have authority?
( both groan )
Okay, that's a hell of a lot
longer than it needed to.
Yep.
It's your fault for not paying
more attention
to the rules
in the first place.
Shiro:
You're turning red.
Sora:
Duh, she's
Shiro: It's 'cause
I took her panties.
Stephanie:
Why are you making me
wear this stuff?
Because we're all wearing
fantasy costumes.
I'm totally digging the 2‐D
effects on her skirt right now.
What does that even mean?!
Anyway, you guys need
to do your job, okay?
Since we haven't had
a king for so long,
our domestic affairs
are a mess.
You handle the internal stuff.
I'm trying to do a no‐item run.
Would you quit using traps?
It works better this way.
This won't do at all.
Unfortunately,
due to the decline of Elkia,
rumors have been spreading
that some of the ministers
are collaborating
with other nations.
As the new king, you need
to make sure that they don't‐
That's all?
Easy solution.
In line with the pledges,
we'll play rock‐paper‐scissors,
and you're gonna
lose on purpose.
I'm scissors.
You're paper.
Whoever loses will be forbidden
from presenting false reports
or arbitrary messages
from here on out.
Do you understand?
We're taking advantage
of the wording in the pledges.
Now there won't be
any more spies.
All right, let's go.
All:
Aschente!
As you can see,
with things being how they are,
our region is in dire need
of provisions.
Right, yeah, okay,
in that case,
here's what you're gonna
need to do.
Yes, sir?
Let's see, we'll introduce
crop‐rotation‐based agriculture.
You'll have one field with...
Wheat, root crops, barley,
and room for pastures.
Sora:
You'll rotate the crops
in that order.
Counselor:
Yes, sir.
Treasury... bonds?
I'll give you
the details later.
You'll issue these bonds
and make the banks buy them.
That'll make a budget
Uh, yes, sir.
Now we just sit back for a few
turns and see how things go.
Stephanie:
Uh, just who are you two, anyway?
You handled all those
problems so easily.
Sora:
Steph, I'm the type
of player who does
all the boring stuff
at once when I play "Civ."
thing I downloaded a ton
of reference texts
while studying for quiz games.
That's not fair, Sora.
You're cheating.
Don't call me a cheater,
not when we're in a world
where cheating means
manipulating
the playing field
with magic.
It looks like
they're ready.
All right,
I guess this is it.
Man:
It's beginning.
Wait a minute,
are you really wearing that?
Why not? Gotta be comfortable
to do my job, don't I?
Shiro:
Sora?
Hmm, if you're ready...
then let's do this.
( all murmuring )
Sora:
Uh...
( clears throat )
( high‐pitched )
Hidey‐ho!
Sora, you're freaking out.
Sora:
Shut up, I'm just as scared
of crowds you are.
I'm just better at faking it.
Huh?
My beloved citizens,
no, my fellow humans,
we Imanity live
in a world
where war is forbidden,
and yet despite this fact,
we have managed to lose
almost all of our lands
to our neighboring nations,
save Elkia,
our final stronghold.
So I ask you now, is it because
our last king failed us?
Because we are the lowest
ranked of all the races?
Because we can't use magic?
Because we are fated
to die helpless?
Not a chance.
No way!
In the ancient war,
the gods, the elves,
the Warbeasts,
and all the other races
battled against each other,
and we not only fought
amongst them,
we lived to survive
to this day!
Do you ever ask yourself
how was it
that this whole continent
was once ruled by humans?
Is it because we are a race
that specialized in violence?
We can't use magic
like the elves.
We're not physically strong
like the Warbeasts.
Nor do we have the longevity
of the Flugel.
So then what made us able
to conquer this land?
We must've been warriors,
right?
Nay, my brethren,
we were able to survive
and to fight...
because we are weak.
In every era and every place,
the strong sharpen their fangs
while the weak
sharpen their intellect.
Then why are we in
such danger now?
It's because the ten pledges
have broken
the banks of the strong
and they have learned
to sharpen their minds
just as we had to
out of necessity.
Now the wisdom,
the strategies that we the weak
once monopolized, the power
to beat all the odds,
the strong have gained
them all!
That's what brought us
to this state.
Now answer me this‐
what makes you bow
your heads like that?
Did you hear me?
Why do you bow your heads?!
You should be proud
to be weak!
We are the weak,
just as we have always been.
Don't you see?
Nothing has changed at all!
True, the stronger races
may imitate our weapons,
but they will never
master them.
Why, you ask?
Because at the heart
of our strength lies
a fearful anxiety
born of our most
humiliating weaknesses.
This fear has given us
the insight to not only escape
from magic but
to learn its secrets.
It has given us the wisdom
of experience
because we must predict
the future to survive!
I say it once more‐
be proud to be weak!
We are the noble weak
who have throughout history
torn out the throats
of those fools
who sit idly by
and boast of their strength.
I hereby declare
as Elkia's 205th king‐
And its queen, too...
Both:
That we will rule
this kingdom together.
It's here.
Each leader of each race
is given their own jewel,
the race piece.
We hereby declare
we'll live as the weak,
protect our weak brethren,
and we will use our wisdom
to make the strong
bow before us!
We are as we once were
and as we will always be.
Hear this, my people,
you are part of a long legacy,
the wisest of the races,
one that could become anything
because we came into
this world with nothing!
( crowd cheers )
Now let's begin this game.
You've suffered enough,
haven't you?
You've endured enough
humiliation, right?
It all ends now.
Are you ready, Imanity?
As of this moment,
my country, Elkia,
will officially
be declaring war
on the rest of the world.
What?!
Let's show them
what we're made of!
We'll take back our land...
Both:
And everything else, too!
( crowd cheers )
Steph:
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What in the world do you think
you're doing?!
( screams )
Oh, my God,
would you relax already?
You're acting all crazy.
How can I be calm
at a time like this?
Declaring war,
are you two trying
to destroy this country
or something?!
Could you please
at least try to think
before you open
your pretty mouth?
How are the other nations
going to view the fact
that we took out the elves?
They'll think were backed by
someone really powerful, see?
Yeah, but still‐
Which means until they know
who that mysterious race is...
They won't be able
to attack us.
Yep, everybody's gonna start
suspecting everybody else,
and they'll all end up
doing nothing.
That's why we took the risk
of declaring war.
And in the meantime,
we'll be able to shore up
the homefront at our leisure.
Cool, huh?
Stephanie:
They put that much
thought into it.
Blank.
Maybe those two
really can do it.
Sora:
So we've gone from our tiny
bedroom to a crappy inn
to Steph's room
and now the royal chambers.
This one's gonna be
the hardest relax in.
The Flugel.
Huh?
Sora:
"Possessing great longevity
and superior
magical capability,
this angelic race lives
on the giant
floating Phantasma
Avant Heim."
"Their insatiable thirst
for knowledge compels them
to challenge others for books
from all over the world."
I bet we could get one of those
guys to come over to our side.
We've got knowledge
from another world, after all.
Wh‐what was that?
Sora...
( laughs )
Well, well.
Looks like things are starting
to get fun, huh?
It's that kid
who thinks he's God.
Oh, please, I don't just
think that I'm God.
I am God, silly.
And you should call me Tet,
remember?
( both scream )
Not again!
How do you like it?
My world, I mean.
Are you enjoying it so far?
Sure, I like your style, kid.
Might be nice if the God
from our world
was as hands‐on as you.
Yeah?
But our enemies can use magic,
something we can't do at all.
Our only remaining
territory is one city.
Our situation
is appallingly bad,
and to protect
the name of Blank,
we can't lose a single game,
that's the world we're in.
What do you think?
It's great.
Isn't it?
Well, awesome,
I guess it was
a good idea to bring
the two of you here
after all, but know this‐
I don't favor
any individual race.
I'm usually
not so hands‐on myself.
Although...
remember what I said.
Everything in this world
is decided by games.
I see.
In other words, even the title
of One True God
is decided by a game.
You got it.
Tet:
That's why I set it up so that
there were exactly 16 races.
Sora:
Each side on a
chess board has 16 pieces.
So I guess defeating
all the races
gives you the right
to challenge God, huh?
Tet:
I love the way
your brain works.
You guys catch on to how things
work here so quick,
it's hard to believe you came
from another world.
Sora:
Why, thank you, God‐dude.
But, hey, careful
what you wish for.
Don't forget
that it's Blank's policy
to be number one
in whatever game we play.
And that attitude is exactly
why I was certain that you
wouldn't be able to resist
the temptation to challenge me.
Now wait a minute,
you do recall
that you lost to us
once already, right?
I do, and that's why
I won't lose next time.
( laughs )
Hey, God‐kid‐
You can call me Tet.
Okay, Tet.
You'd never
lost before, had you?
The God of Play was so very,
very upset at his first loss,
he just had to bring us
here, am I wrong?
Interesting.
What makes you think that?
'Cause I get it.
I know where you're
coming from, bro.
You see,
Blank doesn't lose.
But we've lost to each other
more times than I can count.
You're not allowed
to quit while you're ahead.
( laughs )
Oh, boy, was I ever right
to choose you two crazy kids.
That's right, I don't want you
dropping out of the game,
and I do want a rematch.
Are you disappointed that's the
reason I brought you here?
No way,
I'm actually relieved
it's not some lame‐ass reason
like saving humanity
or something
along those lines.
Well, I'm gonna
head back then. Bye‐bye!
Hey, Tet!
Hmm?
Thanks a lot for dragging us
into this world.
Like, I think this
is where we really belong.
Thanks a bunch.
We owe you.
( laughs )
All:
See you around.
Next time, on the chessboard.
Wait, so that's Tet?
( both sigh )
Steph:
Sora, Shiro!
Hey, don't
tell me that kid
was actually
the One True God!
Yeah, why you ask?
Are you serious?
You said you'd
beat him in a game.
Are you freakin' crazy?!
Forget about it, Steph.
Just get us down from here.
Tet:
Now that we've gotten all the
particulars out of the way,
Please allow me to begin
this tale properly.
Once upon a time...
Sora:
We'll start by
conquering the world,
and then our goal is to
beat God at his own game.
Tet:
Now it's time for
an amazing story,
one I promise
you've never heard before.
( laughs )
Steph:
We sure had fun
last night, didn't we?
Sora:
Oh, yeah, playing games
is the best thing ever.