Hey Patricia...
What are you doing here?
They said something happened...
during a training exercise.
I heard you got hurt...
But you don't look so bad!
This happens all
the time... Really.
Nothing to worry about.
Oh, good.
They let you go because your
eyesight started getting worse?
It's a dog-eat-dog
line of work. Besides...
The squad captain was always
looking for a way
to get rid of me.
Too bad...
But it's not like you
have to quit working
on the force
altogether, do you?
I'm sure they'd let you do some
of the more routine police work.
No way...
Go push pencils behind a desk
or patrol the beat out here?
I think I'll pass. I hate that.
Come on... It's no big deal.
A guy like me has
plenty of options open.
There's the army
airborne division...
or there's the navy
command unit...
Hell, there's even
the military police.
If were up to me,
I'd be fine with you
just being a regular
police officer, Marco.
You would?
I thought you wanted me
to follow my dreams...
Just being a regular cop
isn't even close to
what I want for me.
I'm the kind of person
who needs to see
how far I can push myself.
That's not it... It's just...
I like the gentle Marco better.
Don't worry about a thing...
I'll find a new job before
you can blink an eye.
I have another task for you.
Ask the president
to lay the groundwork
for lifetime senatorship.
He's a popular guy.
He can pull it off.
It looks like this reform
is gonna pass through easily.
I'll make sure of that...
This nation is ailing.
What it needs is a good
dose of antibiotics.
Are you all right, sir?
Yeah.
Tell me you got a shot of that.
Of course.
I want it on the network
news tonight...
And, put some spin on it...
Appeal to people's good nature.
Tell me...
Have they identified
the person responsible?
Just one in a string of
nameless separatists...
Those FRF bastards
won't stop until they've
laid waste to the very
foundations of Italy...
Is that official?
Are we calling this
an act of the FRF?
Why not?
They're radical and violent
and all the people out
there hate them...
They've earned blame.
Since most people
feel this way...
I would suppose
that's the new truth.
What have they
been up to, lately?
We know this much.
Sources say the Milan Group
is clashing behind closed doors.
Take the offensive...
Spread some false information...
Arrest any sympathizers
hiding in the media.
Understood.
How I see the world
is truth to me.
And that truth is enough.
Jose!
Come on down...
You don't have to watch with
the binoculars all the time.
Right! I'll be down in a sec!
Guess it's been about
a month since Milan...
Looks like Angelica's
gonna be just fine.
I don't know, man...
I just know she's
gonna... screw up again.
Come on... Don't say that.
She's on her way out, Jose.
It's not like it used to be.
The girl I knew was never
that good with a gun.
The Angelica I
adored is long gone.
The little girl
that I know today...
Experience tells me
that she'll be dead soon.
Hey...! What's going
on down there?
I'm so sorry, Marco!
If you want to blame
someone, blame me!
I'm the one who
wasn't concentrating.
Angelica... that's
enough for today, alright...?
You can go back to the dorm now.
Right.
It was all meaningless...
Triela...
Please don't touch me!
I... I just want to
be alone for awhile.
What is it Amadeo?
Watcha lookin' at?
It looks like the
princess is feeling down.
So that's what a child
prodigy looks like
when she loses her status.
I never thought one
of the cyborgs
would lose to a flesh
and blood person,
especially not our princess.
Wow, this Pinocchio guy must be
one big monster bad ass, right?
Yeah, some kind of eight foot
tall linebacker or something.
Triela!
What in the world are you
doing up there on the roof?
Get down here...
I have something for you.
And what might that be?
Would you drop the
childish routine, please?
But I am a child.
I went and got you
a new sidearm...
I believe you lost yours
in Montalcino didn't you?
It's a P-232. Same as mine.
It's a nice weapon... Thanks.
Is having your gun taken
that much of a shock
to the system...?
You'll have your chance
to take it back someday.
I won't lose next time.
Oh, yeah. I almost forgot.
I want you to hold onto this.
What is it? Huh?
Angelica!
You on your way back?
Hey...! Yeah, I am.
Hop on. I'll give you a lift.
Oh, no... Did you
hurt your hand?
Yeah... It's nothing...
It'll be back to
normal in no time.
You better hold on tight.
I don't want you falling.
All right. Yes, ma'am.
Angelica, you don't have
to call me ma'am, okay?
Just call me Priscilla
from now on.
Welfare work?
I thought you wanted a job
that's not behind a desk.
Yeah, but the job is in Rome...
not to mention it's twice
what I was making before.
What do you do at the
Social Welfare Agency?
Oh... Look after some kids...
make sure they're staying out
of trouble. Things like that.
You and children...
I never would have thought that.
What are you trying to say?
It's just... I mean you
wanted to push yourself...
I suppose... taking care
of kids is the perfect fit.
Well hey, there, Patricia...
I certainly didn't
expect to see you here.
Leo. Still as stubborn
a mule as ever.
You should know by now...
I'm never going to compromise
myself and sit with you.
You're still heartless...
And the only woman
I've ever known who can
still manage to say no to
Leonardo Conti... ace reporter.
Now be honest... Come on...
You don't have a man
to fill that seat
across from you, do you?
Wait... That's that
fairy tale right...?
I hear it's good.
The Prince of the Pasta Kingdom.
So who's the author?
It's a secret.
How nice...
I happen to have a weakness for
women with secrets you know.
Social Welfare Agency?
Right, what about it?
Nothing... Except that I
know a big secret myself...
Wanna hear?
Yeah, sure.
Truth is... that
Agency's a covert
government
intelligence organization.
I know.
My old boyfriend worked at
the Social Welfare
Agency for a time.
I see...
Then, he was the one who
leaked their secrets to you?
No. He never said a thing.
I knew... I figured it out.
How's that?
It didn't add up...
The guy was a gung-ho member
of the special forces...
There's no way he would ever
switch over to do charity work.
So why did you two split up?
Something in him was hurting.
Who knows...?
It could have been
me who was in pain...
I was afraid of knowing
the truth that he hid.
You look like something's
troubling you, miss.
Can I help you with anything?
You need directions?
Do you not understand Italian?
I do understand... a little bit.
If you're out here
sightseeing...
I can point you in the direction
of all the most popular places.
Thanks... but I'll be fine.
The city's so beautiful...
I can't stop looking.
I'm glad to hear that you
like Italy as much as you do.
The view from here
is a spectacular one.
That's something we
can see eye to eye on.
It's quite a view...
Are you doing a story on
the Social Welfare Agency?
Yeah, and what I'm
piecing together...
is that they raise and train
children to be assassins.
That can't be true.
I haven't heard anything
about that in the news.
The fact that it
isn't in the news
is more proof than
anything else.
Almost all of
the country's media
is controlled by
the prime minister.
Which makes it another
government run organization.
That makes him nothing less
than the 'media king' of Italy.
Right... But I know they
actually do charity work...
I've even gone by to
visit their facilities.
Listen...
I have my own vision, of
how this country should be...
The Public doesn't
care about the truth
only because they
don't know it...
See... I want to lift the veil
that shrouds this country.
Patricia...
I need to ask you if you
would help me with my story.
What?
You're curious about your ex.
I know that you are...
Why else would you carry
that scrap of paper?
You want to know the truth.
Damn spooky, isn't it?
You got your cops,
politicians, city officials...
All of them denying everything
like they all sat
in the same room
to get their stories straight.
Makes me sick to my stomach.
Do you know...? Is it true
about the child assassins?
The editorial department
got an anonymous tip.
This was taken at
a place nearby...
It's not a clear shot,
but you can still make it out.
Hold on... You think...
You think that...
Marco's involved?
Don't have a clue...
Besides there's more than
one brand of justice...
I mean for all we know, he could
be one of the good guys...
You know what would help?
Do you have a photo
of your ex-boyfriend?
Maybe contact info for an
old boss of his or something?
Anything.
Leonardo!
Wow. The editor's in
early for a change.
There's no smoking in here.
It's not lit, genius.
There's a call
waiting for you...
I think it's some
police officer.
Hey, it's Conti.
I wanted to say thank
you for the other day.
I've suddenly remembered a rumor
about the Social Welfare Agency.
This rumor is that they
have a secret office
just outside of Rome...
Suspicious people coming
and going constantly.
I'll check into
that later today.
Thanks for the tip.
No, don't thank me...
I hope you find something.
Is that good enough for ya?
Absolutely, Lieutenant
Colonel... Good enough.
Shame Marco left the force...
But I guess he found
another niche, huh...
He doing a good job?
The investigation's progressing
well, but I need to do some more
research before I can
compile a full report.
Don't push too hard. Let the
information come to you.
Anything you find out about
these government
assassins will help.
So have you worked up a plan to
pull off the kidnapping yet...?
I'm eager to get
my eyes on that...
I don't know.
It's nothing earth shattering.
I doubt it will be enough to
stop the bridge's construction.
At least it should make
for good publicity.
Of course it will.
Listen, I gotta go. My contact's
here. I'll call you later.
Hey, I'm not interrupting am I?
Not at all... Hop on in.
Ready to do some digging?
The place is deserted... great.
Freeze!
Mr. Leonardo Conti...
I'm placing you under arrest.
I've heard a lot
about you, Marco...
How is it you can arrest me when
you're not on the force anymore?
What do you know about me?
Well for one, I know that
you screwed up your life...
And that you joined up
with the wrong side
and broke the heart of a woman.
What are you talking about?
Marco...
Patricia? What the...
Why are you here?
Leonardo and I know each
other through our jobs...
The question is...
Just what in the hell
are you doing here?
Get away from him now!
He's with the Padania!
Leo...
Sorry I used you, sweetheart.
But I had to do
what I had to do.
Then he's telling the truth...
So Marco...
I checked your
background you know.
Central Securities Operations
Service is quite an elite unit.
And yet you quit. Why?
And what about her?
She's nice...
But just like your job,
you quit her too...
Is that how bad you wanted to
do the government's dirty work?
Shut your mouth!
Things aren't like this
because I wanted them to be!
I've had enough of your talk...
So I'm gonna blow your mouth
right off your goddamn face!
You can't make that shot...
Not with that bad
right eye of yours.
It'd be a shame to miss
and hit your princess.
Angelica!
They raise and train
children to be assassins...
Patricia...
You... You can't get any
more involved with this.
Why?
So is doing this the kind of
thing that fulfills your dreams?
Don't you think you've
pushed yourself far enough?!
Listen to me...
I never wanted things to
turn out like this either...
Believe me.
It's hot out here today.
It is, ma'am... Uh, Priscilla.
And so we returned
closer than before.
They've got you housed back in
the dorms now, don't they...?
So what do you guys do for fun?
Having her call me
by my first name...
I wonder how that's
gonna work out.
I'm reading a new book...
It's called "The Prince of Pasta
Kingdom." It's really neat!
So... you like...?
Is it a good read?
Yeah!
If we could only go back to
the way things used to be.
Well we're not
professionals you know
and it's not like the story
has to be complex...
Just think of all the fairy
tales you heard as a kid.
They're all simple and
have memorable characters.
Like, maybe the dragon
that kidnapped the princess
just seems evil at first.
Okay, all done!
I wanted to help you,
but from the looks of it,
you should be protecting me.
Only because you're no good.
And so, after getting
the platinum fork
on the mountain of fire,
the prince safely returned to
the kingdom with the princess.
And all the kingdom rejoiced.
Well, what do you think?
It was wonderful!