It's not even noon...
and you're drinking?
I just feel halfhearted
about the whole thing...
Do you remember
a long time ago,
the first time I
went to see you?
Probably more than
you'd like me to.
You were one
presumptuous young lady.
The only reason I
became an activist
was to restore my
father's honor.
But I think that somewhere
down that righteous path
those pure intentions
might've gotten diluted.
Skirmishing with the government
like we did last night...
that makes me nothing
more than an outlaw.
Sounds to me like you
don't feel you're finished.
Will you come with me?
Of course. I always
have before, haven't I?
I hope we make it in time.
I'm gonna burn up the highway.
You sure you're okay to drive?
Don't worry about it.
I'll sober up along the way.
Triela!
Go ahead, Hilshire...
I've got this one.
Let me help--
Triela, move!
Please, you have
to find Cristiano!
Uncle!
Pinocchio!
Pinocchio...
I just want--
Didn't you hear those
shots being fired...?!
You have to leave! Uncle, now!
I'm not going to
let you die here!
You must listen to me,
Pinocchio...!
I have made up my
mind about this.
I'm leaving.
I'm going into hiding...
Now you need to escape.
You will find a car
hidden in the courtyard...
Use this key.
Pinocchio...! I'm so sorry!
Please forgive me!
Hilshire, come in?
Triela! Are you all right?!
Pinocchio got away from me.
I'm looking for him now.
I'm squaring off with a guard,
second floor, front hallway!
Hilshire!
I'm fine! Just find Pinocchio!
Yes, sir!
I just can't hit him.
You monster...
That's mine!
That's the gun he stole
from me in Montalcino!
How dare he shoot me with the
gun that Hilshire gave to me?!
So who's the real monster here?
As if you would
ever understand...!
I'm obligated to
fight trash like you!
Likewise, little girl!
Alessio, is the car ready?
Alessio?
That's Cristiano. We got him.
Now, put him in the car, Rico.
Yes... Right away.
Ferro!
Yes?
Any signs they
have backup coming?
Not a chance. We've turned
away all incoming vehicles.
Marco, we have
Cristiano in custody.
We'll be taking
the west road out.
Copy that.
Giorgio... We're at
the gate. You see us?
Yes.
Then bring the car.
That's a kid!
Wait...! Franco?!
Rico!
Cristiano, wake up!
Are you all right?!
Get him in the car,
Flanca, now!
I guess I should
thank the two of you.
No... We didn't
come here for you...
We came for Pinocchio.
Where is he?!
He's still at the mansion.
Marco, come in.
I'm here.
The target's been abducted.
He's in a red Alfa Romeo.
They'll be to you
any minute now.
Understood...
We'll stop them cold...
Hey... it's time!
I'm ready.
You have a red car
coming. Stop it!
Yes, sir. I understand.
This is stupid...
Saving me will only make it
worse on the two of you.
Those people will
come after you next.
I thought the only reason
you got into this racket
was to avenge your father.
Yes, it was! But right now,
I'm helping the two of you!
I cannot just abandon you...
Flanc--
Angelica!
Flanca, no...! You have
got to stay with me!
Franco, I'm really cold...
I'm sorry for failing you...
Flanca, slow down. We can't
make the turn at this speed.
You have to slow down!
Hit the brake!
Caterina... You can't die!
Triela!
We pulled the car out
further downstream,
but we haven't found
any bodies yet.
We may have to drag the river.
I see.
We're still searching
the mansion as well...
but it looks like... Cristiano
has disposed of the documents.
He knew we were coming.
Leave the rest to
the Milan branch
and get back to headquarters.
I take it no cyborgs were lost?
No, but two were
seriously injuried.
I'll be sending them
back in the chopper,
so we need to have
headquarters prepped
for site-specific replacement.
Triela.
You shouldn't be so reckless.
You've told me that.
I won...
Yeah.
You should praise me...
That's what you do
when someone wins.
Marco...
Are you injured...? If so, then
you should be on the chopper.
I'm fine, but what
about Triela and Rico?
The chopper's taking
them both to headquarters.
Thankfully...
their injuries don't seem
to be life threatening.
I'm happy for them then.
Marco, I have to
tell you something.
Yeah?
I wanted to say I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
For not being able
to stop the car.
What is with you...?
You're always apologizing,
you know that?
You did a great job, Angelica.
Jean, sir?
We're taking the chopper...
Try not to stand.
Okay.
From the look of it, your
injuries will heal quickly.
And then you can get
back to work for me.
Great!
--Really...?
--Yeah.
It was just another dream.
Hey... Triela, there you are!
So, finish with your treatment?
They sure did. I was
waiting for you to get done.
So let's walk back together.
Cool...
I'm so glad our bodies
are all fixed up again!
Yeah.
Why aren't you happy?
You beat Pinocchio.
You should be thrilled.
I know.
I'm not as happy
as I expected...
I wonder why that is.
It felt like Pinocchio and
I were similar... somehow.
I don't know.
Claes guess what?
Jose told me that Rico and
Triela are coming back today!
Oh... really...?
Isn't that the best
news you've heard?
Yes.
I get really lonely
being the only one here.
Wait!
What's the matter?
I have to go...!
I'm supposed to meet Jose!
I hope you have a good time.
Jose!
I hope I'm not late. Am I?
Not at all, Henrietta.
You're right on time.
Are you ready to go?
Yes!
What?
Here...