I don't understand
why I'm the one
who's having to guard
some stupid little girl.
She's not just
any little girl...
She's Mario Bossi's daughter.
The trial is about to begin.
It would be the absolute worst
time for her to get kidnapped.
But you don't need a cyborg
like me for a job this small.
She's a regular girl
right around your age.
Spending time with her might
be good experience for you.
Oh, you mean because I'm not
a regular girl! I get it!
That didn't go too well.
All she's even willing to do
these days is keep training.
Because of the Pinocchio thing?
Yeah. Taking a hit like that
has been pretty hard on her.
She's got a lot of pride
she's gotta fight through.
So what all do you know
about Bossi's kid anyway?
She's his common-law daughter.
Lives alone in Naples. The
public doesn't know about her.
Still, we're not going
to take any chances.
You know Jose... About Triela...
I'd so much like to show her
more of the world
than this violence.
Augustus...
I'm back home again...
But tomorrow I have to leave
so I can get to know
a "regular" girl.
Of course, Hilshire and
I argued again today...
We always do... even though
I really don't want to.
You want field work?
Hartmann... I am sorry.
But there's other
work for you to do.
You mean Rome,
or Paris, maybe Lisbon?
Or traveling
anywhere in the world
to meet with police
officials...? That work?
Precisely.
Europol is like the European
version of the FBI...
We're hated by
police organizations
everywhere you turn.
Establishing friendly
relationships with them
is a very important job.
I don't care.
Do you realize that over
a million and a half girls are
illegally bought and sold
around the world, every year,
like cattle?!
Why don't you put me on
that task force, Sir?!
Listen Hartmann.
About our little conversation
the other day...
I appreciate your passion...
but I can't give
you any field work.
Why not?
It was requested by the German
police who sent you here.
What the hell...?
Why does that matter?!
You need to refine
your diplomatic skills...
Do that and
you'll be just fine.
You'll get what you
want out of your life.
You can only realize your ideals
once you've laid the foundation.
Here.
What's this?
Watch it and give it
some serious thought.
It's a video depicting a scene
of child abuse we've found.
Have you ever heard
of a snuff film?
It's a video of a murder,
meant for entertainment.
What?
People either abduct the kids,
or buy them and film
them being killed.
I can't believe this.
Some are fakes. A lot
of them are, actually.
But, just like you said,
trafficking continues
every year.
While many children go missing
for good, some are found.
Found as cut-up corpses.
And a small percentage of those
cases are deemed as credible.
This is the reality.
Our world is filled with evil.
Until you can accept that fact,
I can't send you on
field investigations.
You're blessed, kid.
You grew up believing that
people are inherently good.
I envy you for that.
Oh... Hi...!
I'm Maria Machiavelli.
Hello. Victor Hilshire...
This here is Triela.
Ciao!
Nice to meet you.
We'll be your security detail
until your father's
done testifying.
Uh, so...
What do I do when I want to hit
the town and stuff like that?
First off, you don't.
It's best for your safety
if you stay indoors.
I have to go talk
with the Naples D.A.,
so I'm leaving you in charge.
Me? In charge?
When are you going
to be coming back?
Beginning of next week...
And don't worry...
You won't be alone.
Olga and her team
will be staying here.
Say, I got a question.
Yeah, what is it?
I heard that you're
a professional killer.
Is that true?
It is.
Maybe you could show
me one of your tricks.
Well, okay...
So cool!
I got another question.
Yes?
You got time for any hobbies?
Hobbies?
I've been into
football lately...
I play it whenever I can.
No hobbies...
Well... Do you maybe
collect anything?
I do... I have a
teddy bear collection.
Tadah!
Every so often my dad
gives me one. Now...
There's Pepino, Guytano,
Jacinto, Zoff, and Bobo.
And this is Alex.
He's my favorite.
I got him last Christmas...
He's supposed to be
a football forward!
Hey...
I have that same
one at home...!
I also got him as a
present last Christmas.
Yeah...? And what did
ya decide to name yours?
I call him Augustus.
That sure is a strong-sounding
name...! What position is he?
What?
You know Hilshire
told me that you were
the one responsible for saving
my dad's life over the holiday.
Uh, yeah. Ms. Machiavelli--
You can call me Mimi.
Mimi, I'm wondering if
you love your father...?
Because... I know
he's said before
that he hasn't seen his
daughter in a long time.
Do you hold a grudge
against him?
He's my daddy!
Of course I love him!
I'm glad.
I finally feel, like I'm being
useful to Hilshire for once.
Lately, I've been feeling
kind of depressed
because I messed up at work.
I guess you have it pretty
rough with these guys, huh...
But what about you, Mimi...?
I mean you're the one who
has to live all by yourself.
You kidding...? It's a blast.
I can do what I want, no
adults bugging me. I love it.
Checking over and over
won't change it, Pauline.
She was strangled and
died of asphyxiation.
The killer had to
be a large man.
Right... I know.
Sorry, Rachelle, but Agent Alain
kept pestering us
to check again.
He actually thinks it's
the medical examiner's fault
the investigation's
at a standstill?
The guy's trying his hardest...
Maybe you should give
him a break, okay...?
And why don't you
meet him sometime...
He would make quite a catch.
I'm doing fine on my own.
Rachelle, you should try to care
more about meeting new people.
You don't want the opportunity
of finding a man to pass you by.
I suppose you're right.
Maybe I should try.
Victor Hartmann?
Hi. Aren't you with
the Paris police?
My name's Rachelle Belleut...
and you and I work on the same
floor but we haven't spoken...
Do you need something
from me, Rachelle?
I was hoping that you
and I could talk some...
Do you have any
plans this weekend?
My job is to determine
the cause of death
for the children we find...
This one dies of blood loss.
That one was asphyxiated.
And of course, we never
can solve anything...
Even if we have intel
about human trafficking...
Europol has almost no authority
in whichever place
we find it happening.
Oh, uh... I'm sorry.
I've just been
talking your ear off.
No... It's fine.
I think I may have
forgotten how to do this...
It's been a very long time
since I've been on a date.
I even borrowed these
clothes and perfume...
Pretty sad, huh?
Na, it's been a
while for me, too.
I really only dine out
during business meetings
or by myself when I travel.
The chief got on my
case the other day.
Said I knew too little
about the real world
and needed to get out more.
He had a hell of a point.
I vastly underestimated
the scope of the
child abuse situation.
I had no clue that there were
so many people driven by evil.
I couldn't believe it, either.
Until I joined Europol...
I had never seen such
violently mutilated corpses.
And now...
I'm scared at how
used to it I am.
Tell me, Hartmann.
What will you do when you learn
everything about the real world?
Forsake all hope and
return to Germany?
No... I'll cut a deal
with the chief...
I'll do whatever he wants if
it'll put me in the field.
I can't face that the
world is devoid of hope.
Those children need help.
Um, I heard from an Italian
investigator I know,
that the Naples mafia
has recently started
a new vein of their human
trafficking business,
based in Amsterdam.
Of course we can't
investigate it officially...
But we could both go
there... if you'd like.
Excellent vintage.
Machiavelli Chianti
Classico Riserva.
Oh yeah, daddy sent me
a case of that stuff
just because it
matches my last name.
This wine was made by Niccolo
Machiavelli's descendants.
You know that.
Uh... So who is he?
Triela.
A medieval philosopher...
A famous quote of his is
"One must be a fox
to recognize traps,
and a lion to frighten wolves."
Exactly right...
That's impressive, Triela.
Thank you... it was nothing.
Checkmate.
You're better than me at every
game we've played...! Geez!
Want to play foosball again?
Think I'll pass.
I've had my butt handed to me
for three days straight now.
So... Why don't we play a game
of real football outside...
I bet that's something
I can beat you at.
Doesn't matter...
While the trial's on
you have to stay inside.
But I really wanna
see my boyfriend!
Come on...! Pretty please!
You text-message him
constantly as it is.
Yeah, but I wanna see him!
I wanna see him and hug him
and kiss him all over! You know!
Now, I'm sure you could
persuade Hilshire somehow.
No.
Thanks.
I'm curious about something...
Yeah?
I get the feeling that
you're in love with Hilshire.
Why do you say that?
Well, it's obvious enough
to me, at least...
Have you told him?
Of course not...
Because I don't
even know for sure
if the love I'm feeling is real.
Besides, it wouldn't
matter to either of us.
We could never have a
relationship like that.
Yeah, why not...?
You wouldn't be the first
teacher and student
to fall in love.
Just look him in the eye
and say... "Ti amo!"
After that I'm sure
it'll all work out fine.
You may be right.
You know, when she's hanging
around with Mimi like that,
Triela almost seems like
your average teenage girl.
She really does.
After living with Mimi
for several days now,
I've learned that--as much
as I'd like to deny it--
cyborgs are very different
from regular girls.
I know about things
like marksmanship,
firearm maintenance, martial
arts, and lock-picking...
I don't know a
single thing about
the latest music or popular
television programs.
Which means that I have only one
thing that I'm supposed to do.
Hilshire, I can't tell
you how much I appreciate
everything you've
done for my daughter.
It's no problem.
I'm just glad the trial could
come to a close
without incident.
My only hope is that
this can somehow
make amends for
the things I've done.
So what's next...?
Have you given any thought
to where you're going?
I'll escape overseas
like I always have...
And I would think that Mimi
wants to stay in Naples...
so I probably won't
see her for some time.
Too bad.
I was hoping you'd
give Triela my regards.
Nah, forget it...
She probably still considers
me one of the bad guys.
And I can't blame her.
Do you think that mobster from
Naples--that Mario fellow--
you think he was
telling the truth?
It seemed he opposed the
group's human trafficking angle
from the start.
That's not the kind of
business he was into...
He regretted it.
I can't believe behind that door
they're making snuff films.
Hey... Why don't you stay
here and watch my back?
No way... I'm in.
I'm sick of seeing what
they do to these kids.
I never knew how painful
a bullet wound could be.
Rachelle, hold on!
Well, get you outside
and call the cops,
then we can get some help.
We haven't-- We still
haven't found the kids...
We have to help them...
Look, a light!
I'll be back. You don't move.
Have you ever heard
of a snuff film?
It's a video of a murder,
meant for entertainment.
People either abduct the kids
or buy them and film
them being killed.
This is the reality.
Our world is filled with evil.
Rachelle, wait--
Keep watch in the
hallway, Hartmann...
Rachelle!
She's still alive. I have to
try... I have to save her.
I know, Hartmann.
I didn't want to
believe it either...
I had no idea the real
world was this revolting...
Was blind to it.
We've let countless
children die in the past...
But... if I can save this
one girl, just this one...
Then I think I'll actually
be able to believe
that this world isn't completely
devoid of hope... like you said.
Do you believe it, Victor?!
What?
There's still hope in our world!
That it's not completely gone...
Yes, I do!
I believe it because
there're still people
like you in the world!
Rachelle...? Rachelle...?!
Rachelle...! Rachelle!
What do you call that crap?!
You're a disgrace to
the entire squad, soldier!
Put on your equipment.
10 kilometer run! On the double!
Sir!
Now, Triela...
Yes?
I must apologize for how
pathetic my men are.
You must be disappointed he
didn't put up much of a fight.
No, it's okay...
Use this... as an example.
This is what can happen
when even the toughest
of soldiers is
caught off guard, men.
Never lower your guard!
I don't care if your enemy
is bled out and dead.
Until now, you've always
relied on your body's abilities
to overwhelm your opponents.
Which is exactly why you lost
to this Pinocchio fellow.
Was that the kind
of thing you wanted?
She must be pretty
important to you.
She is... That's why
I called you here--
to make her feel some
real pain for once...
She can't train
with agency members
because of her conditioning,
so you're all I've got.
Plus we don't have any guys
around here of your caliber.
The whole exercise should
be a good bit of training
for my men as well.
Terrorists these days
aren't always adults
with scowls on their faces...
As for your girl there...
She's gonna be just fine.
In two weeks I'll change
that bunny rabbit
into an unstoppable force.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
Is the patient fully under?
Yes.
Alright. It's a routine
leg replacement. Let's go.
This new leg has a much
better performance level
than her previous one.
That so?
The development stage has
gone much more smoothly...
Ever since we started using
Claes for all the testing.
Donato, look...
Yes, what's the problem?
The cyborg it's... it's crying.
Just wipe them away.
Sir?
Wipe off the tears. It's normal.
They shed them in
their sleep sometimes.
You awake?
We've finished your maintenance,
so you can leave here as
soon as you can walk out.
What's with the tears...? You
have a bad dream or something?
I can't... really remember.
It seemed kind of
like a dream...
In it, I met my mother.
I know she was
wearing glasses...
And she had on the sweetest
smelling perfume...
She was saying something
I couldn't understand.
Then, right before I woke up,
she came down and gave
me a very gentle hug.