What I'd really like is
for Jose to care for me
even more than he already does.
Do you think if I told him that,
it would make him not like me?
I aware that I'm treated much
better than the other girls...!
Dr. Bianchi... Do you think
I'm being selfish about this?
Don't worry about it.
There's nothing wrong
with feeling this way.
Brother!
I heard you're going
to the Balkans.
Is that true, Jose?
I'll be back before
you know it...
It'll only be six months.
But no...!
They say the radiation
is too dangerous.
Don't worry.
You won't get lonely.
Our brother will be here.
But he might as well not be.
Jean never comes to my recitals.
But you're always there.
I get the feeling from father
and mother and Jean...
that work is more important to
them than anything that I do...
All they ever do is leave
me at home all by myself.
That's not true.
They all love you more
than you could ever imagine.
When I grow up I'm going to
join the military police...!
That way, you and
I will always be--
Being an M.P. in this
country isn't great...
It's very dangerous.
Just stick with being a harp
soloist, Enrica. Alright?
Just a dream...
You awake, Jose?
Why don't you go to bed if
you're planning on sleeping.
Yeah, I think I will.
I'm meeting
Marcantonio tomorrow.
Second Lieutenant Abbado?
You joined the MP's together.
So how long's it been?
Five or six years...
I haven't seen him
since my discharge.
Whoa, Jose. You're getting
kinda shaggy on top.
So what do you do
these days? PMC work?
No... not close...
A buddy hooked me up
with public welfare.
Seriously?
Is that strange?
Yeah, guess that whole incident
must've been pretty hard on you.
Yeah, it was...
You wouldn't believe.
Everything I heard about
that whole mess was crazy...
It makes total sense to me
why you and your brother
quit the military police.
Enough about me.
How are things with you?
I assume you're still involved
with the First
Parachute Regiment?
Oh, no... I'm the leader of
a patrol squad in Molise...
We uh, handle
kidnappings and smuggling.
You? Commanding a
reconnaissance squad?
That funny?
The only reason I
wound up with the job
is because you bailed on us...
Listen, I had the easy life when
you were head of the class...
Back in the days
of our Balkans PKF.
How's your mother doing?
I always loved her cooking...
She made the best salsichia.
She's dead.
Year before last, she was
in a demonstration...
A tear gas round hit her
on the head, and killed her.
I'm sorry...
Who was it that
played the harp...?
Wasn't it your sister?
It was.
Oh my god!
Terrorists.
Of course.
Miss, you're all right.
Come on stand up.
We gotta move.
Beatrice. He's headed
your way. Slow him down.
Understood, Sir.
Hey Bea... Smell him.
Yes, sir.
Military grade explosives.
So you're the one behind
yesterday's bombing.
Answer me or I'll make it hurt.
Not so fast, Jean...
Why don't we go take a look
at this idiot's place first...
After all, he's a
blue... A Padania.
Which means he's hiding some
kind of evidence somewhere.
Did you find it, Bea?
Yes.
Here.
Wanna tell me how
you acquired this...?
Only military men
can get their hands
on such high-grade explosives.
Rico.
Do you want me to get started?
I want you to hurt him
until he decides to talk.
Yes, sir.
I feel bad for him.
He's committed a
serious offense...
He can feel bad for
himself behind bars.
She keeps that up in there,
and they'll learn real quick
that you can't
question a dead guy.
Jose...
Is that the river Princess Ann
swam in in 'Roman Holiday'?
It sure is.
Then is that bridge where
she fought using the guitar?!
Yes. That's right.
Castel Sant'Angelo...
Sucha beautiful place.
I think Tosca also takes
place in this castle.
Tosca?
Yeah, it's an opera.
The last scene takes place
by that big angel statue.
There's a Colonel Gagne
who's the supervisor of
military logistics in Molise.
I've heard the nasty
rumors for some time now
that he's been funneling
weapons to the black market.
The Padania has been
exceptionally well-armed
since the beginning
of this year...
Just last week we uncovered
a large amount of
military-grade explosives.
We need proof...
Find that and the
military police will be
forced to approve of the
colonel's assassination.
Understood, sir.
At what point do you
think this will ever end?
When will what end,
Lieutenant Colonel?
The fighting, the madness.
Do you remember the
Balkans conflict...?
We fought under those gray skies
together for two whole years.
And against whom?
At the time, we didn't
have the slightest idea
who we were fighting.
Who was the enemy?
It was an
ethnic conflict...
We had to consider every
armed person an enemy.
You're wrong...
The adversary we fought
was hate itself...
So it makes perfect sense
that we have nothing to show
for all of our efforts.
We can only keep hate
buried for so long at a time.
The end will come someday.
Do you actually believe that?
I have to.
What other choice do
we have than to fight?
You're right.
That's all we can do...
or know to do.
Castel Sant'Angelo?
That's right.
Henrietta loves Princess Ann,
so she thought it was like
the greatest thing ever.
I believe Tosca better
represents Sant'Angelo.
The opera...?
Did you see it on video?
I did...
and I thought how
Henrietta would cry
if she heard the words.
Like, "I lived for my art,
I lived for love..."
Wait... How's it go again?
I lived for my art,
I lived for love,
I never did harm
to a living soul.
With a secret hand I relieved as
many misfortunes as I knew of.
Always with true faith my prayer
rose to the holy shrines.
Always with true faith
I gave flowers to the altar.
I gave jewels for
the Madonna's mantle,
and I gave my song to the stars,
to heaven, which
smiled with more beauty.
In the hour of grief...
Why, why, o Lord, ah,
why do you reward me thus?
Tosca takes place
200 years ago...
while Rome is under
a reign of terror.
A singer named Tosca
is the main character...
As for the story, Tosca's
lover Mario is arrested
and sentenced to death for
harboring a political criminal.
So she goes to the head
of the secret police,
Baron Scarpia,
to beg for Mario's life.
That's the basic premise.
You seem to know
a lot about it...
Have you always liked the opera?
Not really...
I wouldn't say I'm the type.
I saw it with a friend
of mine a long time ago.
All of the main
characters in Tosca
wind up dying by the end of it.
The same thing happens
in every Italian opera...
Murder, illness,
revenge, suicide...
People just keep dying
and dying and dying!
And do you happen to know
what that means, Beatrice?
I can't say I do.
It means Italians love tragedy.
They're sentimental about
everything, especially death.
That's why our cities are filled
with violence and vengeance.
That's why every solution we
devise is rooted in bloodshed.
I don't know, Bianchi...
It's been a lot more
exhausting than usually lately.
What has?
Henrietta and I can't
talk about anything real...
It's always just
stars and myths...
And the presents are
just a formality...
There's no true sincerety.
The poor kid's
starved for love...
I don't think it's
that big a deal Jose.
What's so wrong with
fulfilling that need for her?
What's the matter?
I was just thinking
about my little sister.
She spent a lot of her
time at home all alone.
The rest of us were too busy
with whatever we were doing...
I think we made her feel lonely.
And you wish you
could take it back?
Yeah.
Be clever like a snake...
but also be simple
like a pigeon.
Uh... What's that?
It's an attitude you should
use to survive this world.
Well that's Easier
said than done, doc.
There's nothing wrong
with taking your time
to think over delicate matters.
It's a waste to feel
shame for acting shrewdly.
The answer's quite simple...
Basically... Just don't
think about it so hard.
I'll try.
Jean, the army truck just
made it through the pass.
I copy that, Ferro. Stop all
subsequent vehicles you see.
Roger.
What's the plan...?
Do we capture them or not?
If they concede,
we capture them.
Even if we kill them all,
the scene itself should
be proof enough.
You gotta be kidding...
Stop the truck!
Turn off the engine and
stay inside the vehicle!
Give us your names,
ranks, and cargo!
Go, now!
Hilshire! Do it!
Take the shot.
Yes, sir.
Jose, what did you
think of my shooting?
I hit the target every time,
and, uh... did you...
Yeah.
Turn around.
And one more time around.
It's not too tight, is it?
No.
And in the shoulders?
Feels fine.
Henrietta... Is that your dress?
Yeah.
Skirts are fun for a change...
They make neat
sounds when you move
Marcantonio blamed
the government
for his mother's death
and turned traitor.
It was easy for him
to assemble his team.
There are plenty
like him out there...
From then on, they worked
for Colonel Gagne
smuggling weapons off-duty.
The colonel's assassination
has been approved...
We'll do it next week.
He'll be here to see an opera.
I'll be there.
Jose... I can do this
one on my own, if you want.
No, I'll be fine...
It's not like it's worth
getting depressed over.
None of this ever is.
I guess this is my 'Clever
like a snake' time... Right...
There's nothing wrong
with taking your time
to think over delicate matters.
It's a waste to feel shame
for acting shrewdly.
Beautiful.
Jose...
Now, go on.
Yes, sir!
We're home!
Welcome back...
Did you two enjoy the opera?
We were working the whole time
so we didn't get
to see very much.
Right, I should have known that.
It's too bad though.
Tosca is quite a moving story.
I only got to see
the first part.
I have a question.
Rico, were you moved?
It kinda scared me how
loud it was in there.
Hey... Guess what, Rico.
In the theater when Jose saw
me, he said I was beautiful!
That's great!
The only thing Jean said to me
was, "It doesn't suit you."
"I lived for my art,
I lived for love."
So, tell me. What did you
think of the opera, Enrica?
D'you Still think
you're too young?
No, I had a really great time!
Excellent. I'm glad.
In fact, Jose...
I think I'm going to
be a harp soloist!
Someday, I'm going to play
my harp in this very theater!
Of course you will...
And I'll be there.
So when that day comes, you
have to make sure you bring
Mother, Father, and Jean
with you to watch me, okay?!
I will...! It's a promise!