Yes?
Good morning, ma'am.
Sorry it's so early...
It's Vincenzo... I'm here
to pick up your husband.
Well good morning, Vinci...
Would you like to
wait inside for him?
Thank you, but I think
I'll just wait here.
So, have you gotten the
hang of your new job?
Just about.
Well, hurry up and
learn so my husband
can take a few days off
and relax for a change.
Bruno! Vinci's out
front waiting for you.
Okay.
I'll see you after
school, Antonio.
Now, study hard
and make me proud.
So is that all we have on the
books for this month or what?
The guy we have in
back is the last one.
But you are
scheduled for lunch...
You're dining with
Cristiano at 1:30 at Attoria.
I almost forgot.
And while the two of
you are having lunch,
I'll go over to Turin and get
us our next car and number.
You know you're a hell
of a lot more helpful
than I thought you would've
been when you started.
I didn't have a choice but
to pick up things fast...
We don't have a whole
lot of down time.
You're right... Business is
booming, but body disposal
isn't the most productive
work we could be doing.
If people could just solve their
differences with conversation,
the whole world
could get more done.
If only...
But killing's still the easiest
way to solve a problem.
Yeah... as sad a
statement as that is.
Let me ask you something...
If you have that
much disdain for it,
then why do you do this work?
Because you can't support
a family on ideals alone.
We all do the best we can.
I love traveling by train.
Me, too.
I'm real glad you
got better, Angelica.
Angelica?
Yes?
Have you taken
your medication yet?
No, not yet, but I will.
Take it now while there's
still a little time.
You brought Angelica with us and
she's still on medication?
She can't kick the
dependency that fast...
The doc prescribed it...
It's just a little something
to help her along...
Then you need to be
extra careful on this job.
I don't want any BS.
Keep an eye on her.
Got it.
We'll see you two in a while.
I've got an old contact here I'm
gonna hit up for information.
What about you?
You're going to the police...?
I have an old
underground connection...
I need to find out more
about this "Milan Group."
Then we'll meet you back at the
hotel tonight sometime after 6.
You wait right here
until I get back.
I don't want to bother
with any explanations.
Right.
Inspector Moro...
Someone here to see you, sir.
It's not on my schedule...
Tell whoever it is they'll
have to make an appointment.
I don't think you'll
mind, Inspector.
It's your old friend Marco...
Marco... Toni?
Wait, you mean "Leatherhead"
Marco Toni's here?
So what did he mean?
Why'd he call that
guy "Leatherhead"?
National Securities
Operations Service...
known as NOCS for short...
He's an old pro that
used to work here
teaching combat skills.
Guess he's a tough guy...
Marco, my good man!
It's been a hell of a long time.
Looks like you're
doing well, Inspector.
I heard you quit because
of your injured eye.
That true...? What are you
doing these days anyway?
Just running odd jobs
for the Cabinet Office.
It's work for the braindead.
Pinocchio?
Sorry, but I can't say that
I've ever heard of him.
Seems he's been busy killing off
people associated to a trial...
You know, the trial of
that rich guy in Milan.
Ah... I've
heard of that...
The F.R.F. has
way too much power
and influence in this region.
Word around the campfire
is they're greasing
our commissioner's palm so much
we can't conduct any
serious investigations.
Can you give me some
info on anybody...
Even someone on the bottom rung.
I don't know what you're
really doing here...
and I'm not gonna ask ya.
But I will tell ya, the second
you step outside this station,
open those eyes
in the back of your head.
I wonder if Angelica's working
harder now than before.
You're a curious person.
Some might even say nosy...
Traveling all this way to Milan
on your time off just
to check in on her.
Come on. Like you're
not worried too, Olga.
This is her first time
out in quite a while.
What do you think...?
Has she had enough
time to recover
so she can focus on the work?
I don't know. But I think
leaving Marco and Jean in charge
is a bad idea...
After all Marco's the one--
Hey... What are you
two doing here?
Oh, Buon giorno, Marco.
How-How you doin'...?
Uh, Ciao, Angelica.
It's nice to see
you here, Priscilla.
Yeah, we're just here to do a
little shopping on our day off.
You know, girl stuff.
So... Is the job going alright?
Your timing's perfect.
Switch seats with Olga.
Huh?
After I stopped by
the police station,
the "separatists" sent
a tail to keep an eye on me.
He just won't give up.
I can't get anything done.
Okay Olga...
Let's put those ambassadorial
driving techniques to good use.
Right. Consider it done.
Lost him... Got anything
else you need help with?
As long as you're offering.
I assume you two are armed.
We're gonna need firepower.
We both have our sidearms.
Angelica?
Yes, sir.
Don't argue, but I want you to
give your case to Priscilla.
You're gonna sit this one out
and watch from the sidelines.
No, please, you don't need
to give that thing to me...
Submachine guns really
aren't my thing.
Well, they are now.
Just take it.
This isn't a game.
You've got about
three seconds to tell me
exactly what you know.
Please! We don't know
anything, I swear!
We just run errands for
the rest of 'em!! Really!
But you have to know where
I can find your superiors...
And don't make me ask
the question again...
I start repeating myself and
my trigger finger gets itchy.
Fine I'll talk! I'll talk!
There's an apartment.
Our bosses use it as a base.
Like a safehouse.
That's all I know!
Excellent. Now tell
me where it is.
Angelica!
What are you doing?
Let's get going.
After today, I can
finally take a real break.
My son and I are gonna
take a father/son vacation.
With Easter coming up
that should be nice...
I want to thank you for all
of your hard work lately.
I know I shouldn't criticize,
but haven't you been
killing a bit much lately?
We follow the flow.
The government started it.
If they would play by the rules,
we wouldn't behave this way.
But they illegally
harass and arrest us.
Now they're trying to pass
bills to make that legal.
You mean the revised
Anti-Terrorist Special
Measures Law?
I bet things are just gonna
get uglier after that.
Unfortunately...
Milan is poised to become the
Belfast of the 21st Century.
If that happens, you'll have
a decade's long civil war
on your hands that
won't ebb until
both sides are worn
down into the mud.
Do you really want that?
Irredeemable fools exist in
all such times in history.
Words mean nothing
to these people.
They understand only action.
When your vacation is over,
I need you to go and
visit with Pinocchio.
I think it would be
best for the boy
if you'd go and
visit him yourself...
He tries to hide it,
but he'd like nothing more
than to see you face to face.
That boy is a grown man now...
This independence is
the best thing for him.
It doesn't matter if the
kid's sixty years old,
a parent is still a parent
until the day they die...
Well... I should be going...
I still need to swing through
Turin to pick up Vinci.
How does it look?
The business is registered as
an auto parts subcontractor.
We've only seen people
using the fourth floor.
Every other floor in the
building appears to be empty.
It's obviously a nest,
but there are only
four or five people in
it at any given time...
What's the call, Marco?
Four or five people's
not a problem.
Priscilla, go in
the instrument case
and get out the stun grenades.
I've been carrying
that around in here?!
Of course you've been...!
I told you, this isn't a game!
Whoa.
You're not one for
the small talk are you?
Would you rather
I ring the doorbell
and come in for a chat first?
Hey, Priscilla!
The room's clean!
You can come on inside now!
Why don't you and I
stay here, Angelica?
Angelica?
Hey, what's wrong? You okay?
You look flushed.
You should get some rest.
Angelica, don't do that.
You're strong. It hurts
when you squeeze that hard.
Okay?
Let go, Angelica.
Please...
Hey...
Angelica!
Marco...! Help...
Help how...? What's wrong?!
I need to take my pills.
I need my medication. Now!
Is it her dependency?
I don't know.
She's been taking what
the doctor gave her, but...
I just don't know
if it's helping her.
Hey Olga...
Take those guys downstairs
and throw them in the car...
Got it.
Marco...
She didn't hurt you, did she?
Marco, you have
to listen to me...
You can't tell
Jean about Angelica.
What?
If he hears about this,
she'll be hospitalized again.
I just feel so bad for her.
She hasn't done anything wrong.
We're the ones to blame here.
Not one of these girls
deserves what they get...
It's on us...
every last bit of it.
She seems fine.
I think it was just the anxiety
of her first real
action in a while.
If she wakes up without
any more problems,
I want you to give her a gun.
That should help
calm her nerves.
What do we do now?
We torture the captives until
they give up their superiors.
We'll call for help from Rome
and clean house before dawn.
Sounds good to me.
I hear Pricialla ended up with
a broken arm when it was over.
Yeah, she did.
But I gotta say, she took
it all like a real trooper...
That girl is a lot stronger
than you think she is, Marco.
She claims all her strength
comes from the "power of love."
Funny...
I guess at the end of the day,
she's just a dreamer...
I don't know.
She told me herself one day...
"Angelica has
turned out this way
because Marco lacks
any ability to love."
What's the hell is
that supposed to mean?
This is the young things
first job in a long time.
You should try to be
nice to her, at least.
It's easy for you to say that
when you're looking
in from the outside.
Priscilla did all she
could to stop Angelica.
She kept telling
her it hurt, but,
Angelica only snapped out of it
when she heard your voice...
You should let that sink in.
Wow, what a waste. Fainting
on a big trip like this.
I'm really sorry
that happened to you.
No... It's okay...
Marco has been extra nice
to me since it all happened.
Rico... Could I ask you a favor?
Sure, what is it?
Will you let me kill one
of the bad guys tomorrow?
Of course. It'd be my pleasure.
Why the hell do they
need us at the factory?
This is entirely too
far out of the way.
Well, you know they must have
screwed something
up once again...
These guys can't seem
to get anything right
the first time around.
That's true...
I guess you finally
earned the right to talk.
This is Tifosi to Mahdena 01.
We've acquired target heading
south on the Viale Italia.
Contact with 01 in 20 seconds.
No civilian traffic
within 200 meters.
So are you still seeing
that French woman?
I forget what her name was...
Her name's Aline, and yes...
We've been together a while now.
I never saw what was so
great about French women.
You should stick with a healthy
Italian woman from Milan.
Modena 01 to 04 and 05...
Are you ready to move?
Yeah.
We're a go here, Jean.
Now, I want you to listen...
Promise me you'll do it just
like you did in training.
I don't want you killing anyone.
Yes, sir.
That was way too close for me.
Vinchi! Keep your head down!
The car's armored.
Angelica...
Uh, yes sir?
Tell me...
Are you feeling all right
after all that just happened?
I'm fine.
But I'm so sorry I failed you...
I didn't mean to, Marco.
It was an armored Ferrari.
There's not much
you could've done.
But... you moved fast
and you hit everything
you were aiming for...
You did a great job today.
No way...
Please tell me I'm
having a bad dream...
This is such a
fucked up... world.
Rico!
I'm sorry about the
way this turned out...
I didn't mean to break
my promise to you.
No, it's okay...
When it was over,
Marco was happy...
He said that I did a great job!
That's great. I'm really
happy for you Angelica.