Caterina! You're here!
Domenico! Paola...!
It's been a long time.
How many years has it been...?
I was so thrilled to hear
your dear voice on the phone...
Sorry to give you
so little notice...
But my friends and I need
to stay here for a while.
Oh, certainly!
You kids make
yourselves right at home.
Listen, Franco... I just...
I wanna say thanks
for taking care of her.
No need... It's the
other way around.
She takes care of me.
This is Pinocchio...
He'll be working with
Flanca and me for a while.
It's very nice to meet you.
Where are we?
Flanca's vineyard.
That couple you just met,
they're in charge of
running the place.
They make a pretty
fantastic white wine here.
I've never been
a big fan of wine.
Most likely, it was the
same Social Welfare Agency
you ran into in Montalcino.
They're hindering our activities
all around the country.
We're at my vineyard...
We should be safe
here for now, so...
I think we'll set up shop
and plan out the
bridge bombing here.
Fine, you do that.
But if anything happens,
you call the usual number.
Right. Well, do you want
to talk to Pinocchio?
No, that's alright.
I'll just leave him
in your capable hands.
Oh, One more thing...
I was curious about
that pendant he wears...
Is it very important to him?
It's something I gave
to him a long time ago.
Oh.
You should know...
We have a kidnapping plan
underway in Rome now...
The chairwoman of the
Messina Bridge
Development Corporation...
The success or failure of this
will change some future plans.
Yeah, I bet.
The operation is being led by
someone you may have met before.
From Bergamo. Nino Ferretti.
Nino?
There it is.
The chairwoman's car.
Looks like there's no
escort with her today...
Good.
That lady gets more
naïve by the day...
Tell Cosimo and Corra to follow
her no matter where she goes.
Leone.
I just talked with Sergio...
he said her security detail
is being replaced soon...
We need to keep our guard up
until we know who they are.
Come on, Nino.
Don't you think we need to be
a little more proactive here?
I don't think there's
anything more proactive
than being careful.
Uh, that's the end.
Thank you, young lady...
That was the
loveliest performance.
You see...?
She appears as any
ordinary schoolgirl.
Truly, I'm in shock.
That girl has a mechanical body?
We use medical
reconstruction techniques
and new industrial
technologies
in order to fashion
the most lifelike being.
Their skin, bones, and muscles
are made of revolutionary
new materials.
It doesn't make
them 'superhuman',
but they're stronger and
quicker than the average person,
and they obey orders
unquestionably.
But still, there's the moral
issue of using children.
Unfortunately, the
younger the patient,
the more adaptable the brain.
Isabella. We should
only focus on one thing here.
Our national security is key...
That is how we maintain
society's peace of mind.
I don't have the
kind of background
in public safety that you do...
This is difficult
for me to accept...
Chairwoman...
Our medical reconstruction
techniques are the best,
the most advanced in the world.
The state of the
art in science...
The reason for this is
that our cybernetic research
also benefits society
as a whole...
Currently, we provide hundreds
of patients around the country
with artificial limbs
at no cost to them.
And I promise you
that it won't be long
until we develop the same kind
of treatment for you legs.
I sympathize with the
children's plight, I do.
But just think of how many more
can be saved because of them.
We're still running
background checks
on everyone close
to the chairwoman.
Should be done in a few days.
That Padania agent that
we caught the other day...
He talked. He said that the
kidnapping is imminent...
So lets hurry things up.
It's my top priority.
Jose!
Hi, Henrietta. That
was a very nice performance.
You're getting better.
I practice every day.
Hey, Henrietta...
What's that thing?
A kaleidoscope. Jose got
it for me when he was in France.
Is it like a fancy gun scope?
Come here, see for yourself.
Turn this wheel to
change the colors.
Pretty...
Rico... what did you do?
Oh, I'm sorry, Henrietta.
Why did you turn
the wheel so hard?!
Henrietta, did you say
something mean to Rico?
She didn't mean to break it, so
you need to forgive her, okay?
I'm the one to blame,
if anybody.
Lousy antique shop owner...
Jose... No, you didn't
do anything wrong.
I'm going to get
it repaired... but...
afterwards you need
to make up with Rico.
Hey... Show me a
smile there, would ya?
Yes, sir...
Ludovico here.
Still no change at the
chairwoman's estate.
How can I help you?
Someone told me I could get
an antique repaired here.
Is that right?
Sure. We can fix
almost anything.
So, what do you have?
Interesting.
You don't see this kind of
kaleidoscope every day.
My hands are pretty full...
so it might take some time
to get to it, but I'll fix it.
Is that okay?
I guess it'll have to do.
Forget about it... I'll have
it done in three days.
Hired hands like me get
stuck in a rut sometimes...
We need to be reminded
our job's worthwhile.
Besides, I can't let
the girl get more upset.
One mundane afternoon,
a teary-eyed girl
showed up with a
broken kaleidoscope.
She had the faintest
but distinct scent
of pine resin to her.
The kind of resin that is
probably used on violin bows.
There's just such a sense of
drama to it, you know...?
Jobs like that are
the ones that I love.
How's the security issue
look to you, Alfonso?
The bulletproof exterior
is going to work just fine.
Inside... we'll turn
off the drivers side airbag
and then install some
kind of fire extinguisher.
Sounds good.
Well, I'm here. I thought you
had everything you needed.
Tell me, Kaschmann...
Why doesn't she bring
any escorts with her
when she's on the move?
She considers, the excessive
security unnecessary.
That seems a little odd...
Her husband died in
a terrorist attack.
So then... Is there
anything else I can do
to help you out
with all of this?
No, thank you.
We'll handle the entire
operation from here...
Notify the mansion's
security staff
that they're on
vacation as of now.
Oh, thank you, Henrietta.
It looks as if you're starting
a war from this room.
Ms. D'Angelo...
The Five Republics Faction
is out to kill you...
All these weapons are to
prevent that from hapenning.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
If the sight of all this
is too much for you,
I recommend you
close your eyes...
Like it or not, ma'am,
this is our job...
I know... And I'm sorry.
I think I made him angry.
Jose... I only
realized it now...
It's because of what happened
to his family years ago.
It's scary...
As if I could see the color
of hatred boiling inside him...
Jose is a nice person!
Yesterday, even though he
was overloaded with work,
he still made time to take me
to have my kaleidoscope fixed!
There's not a person
in the entire country
who's as nice as Jose!
Is that so...? Then I apoligize.
His hatred must have only
changed him quietly,
on the inside.
Ms D'Angelo... Don't you hate
terrorists like everyone else?
I suppose I did a
long, long time ago...
And what about you, dear?
It's not exactly hate...
I just have a good
reason to kill them.
It's because...
That's exactly what Jose wants.
I've lost my certainty...
I wanted to fulfill
my husband's wish...
But I don't know if
finishing the bridge
is worth any of this...
Is it worth it to shed this much
blood over any mere project?
Nino.
Don't tell me you've fixed
the kaleidoscope already.
Yeah...
The spindle broke off, so I
just whipped up a new one.
Oh...? Pretty slick, genius.
Where'd you learn that one?
I used to tinker with
these kinds of things
back when I was a kid.
Take a look at this down here.
It's fascinating stuff.
You're screwing with me.
This says 'Balzac' on it.
"Lily of the Valley", 1836.
May be a worthless knock off,
but it's nicely-done.
Yeah.
Does the client know
it's a piece of junk?
I'm pretty sure he does... Yeah.
He seemed like he could
appreciate a good joke.
With a gift like this...
it's the thought that
matters most of all.
Flanca...
I've heard stories about
you recent exploits.
And how is Franco doing?
Fine.
To be honest, I never
thought he would be up to
handling any
woman for long...
I guess in the end I
was wrong about the guy.
I talked to Cristiano
the other day...
Don't tell me you've really
given up bomb-making?
But I have.
Because there's a little job
where I could use
your assistance. With you--
The Messina Bridge. I know.
You want the passion
of the planners
to match the size of the job.
Something that
big'll take a lot.
You have enough by yourself.
But you...
I thought you're in this
to avenge your brother.
I used to be...
Hey, you know what the
guys in the business
call me these days...?
They call me the Tibetan Terrier
that can no longer run.
I'll be in Rome for
the next few days.
Call me if you change your mind.
Whatcha see Nino?
Who's the little girl
in the backseat?
According to Sergio,
she's a relative of D'Angelo...
She's visiting Rome on vacation.
Is that right?
Yeah?
Nino.
The authorities caught him.
Our associate at the magazine.
I see... Well... now
it's only a matter of time
before they learn
about this kidnapping.
What do you think? Should we
do it first thing in the A.M.?
The plan's off, Leone.
What do you mean?!
The man... the one who
just got out of the car...
I know who he is.
He's sharp.
He used to be part of
the Ministry of Interior's
anti-terrorism unit.
The risk is too high.
We're done here...
Go gather the others.
This is bullshit.
If we had moved sooner,
we'd be past all this!
Why do you think that Milan
chose Nino instead of you?!
Because he's cautious and he
hates any unnecessary bloodshed.
Leone... You and Nino go
pretty far back, don't you?
The first time he and I met...
he was only a young student
at the Turin
Polytechnic Labratories.
He and his brother would craft
the most creative bombs,
blowing things up at random.
Still, he was a reliable friend.
Is that so...
But after the police
killed his brother,
something in him changed.
He grew more timid.
Those around him even started
calling him the Tibetan Terrier.
Tibetan Terrier?
It's an ornamental
dog from Tibet.
Like a Lhasa Apso.
Alert and agile, but docile.
I don't understand...
We're all capable adults.
Why don't we kill her ourselves?
I'm considering that.
We have no need
for cowards here.
Everything okay, Kaschmann?
I thought you were supposed
to be going on vacation?
Five years I've been in
charge of her security...
I get the feeling...
I wouldn't know what do with
myself out there all alone.
Who's the little girl you got
pushing Ms. D'Angelo around?
She's one of the chairwoman's
relatives, in from Padua.
Well, that's strange.
Cuz in five years I
haven't heard one thing
about any relatives from Padua.
I can't imagine you'd care
about her family, Kaschmann...
or should I call
you Sergio Aimaro?!
We had our guys run
background checks...
We knew everything about
you before we got here.
After tapping every phone line,
inspecting every bank account,
and scouring all the public
records we could dig up...
we learned that you're
actually a Padania agent
who's changed his name and
his face two times so far.
At least now we don't
have to smoke him out...
Ferro. We'll use him
for the decoy operation.
Understood.
According to Sergio,
we've got ten minutes
until the chairwoman's car
pulls up to the steps
of the church.
Of course, she doesn't
have the use of her legs,
so she'll be the most vulnerable
as she's exiting the vehicle.
The focus is on kidnapping
the chairwoman and the girl.
Kill all the escorts.
Dammit!
Now! Move in!
Rico... You shouldn't
have fired the second round.
Right... I'm sorry
for that, Jean.
I can't go on as an
activist any longer.
Ever since my brother died...
I keep asking myself
the same question...
if what we're doing
is truly worth killing
over... I don't know.
Nino...
There used to be a time when
I wouldn't have given
it a second thought.
I don't like this.
I can't imagine you would.
But someday... you'll get it.
How can you be so sure?
Flanca, what is it
you're fighting against?
Do you even know when
victory will be yours?
If you're in this to
avenge your old man...
How many people have to
die to set things right?
Think that over now, while
you've still got the time.
Don't wait until you're
an old dog like me
who doesn't have it in him
to keep running anymore.
What do you think?
Looks good all fixed up.
Maybe even better than
when you brought it in.
Now, young lady...
Make sure you oil
that thing regularly.
Okay!
Uh, sir... The
gentleman who repaired this,
does he happen to
be working today?
I'd really like to thank him.
Oh...
Sorry- Nino quit when he
finished the kalediscope.
He was very talented and
I hated seeing him go.