Do Hilshire's presents not
make you happy anymore?
He doesn't even
care what I like.
He just gets me the
same thing every year.
Triela.
No more shooting
without my permission.
If that's the case...
Then what's stopping
you from increasing
the level of my conditioning?
Hold down the fort, alright?
Will do.
Alright...
So what kind of things should
I work on today then?
A Public Safety investigator
has disappeared in the north.
That's why I'm asking all
of the members of Section 2
to head up there and
take a good look around.
So you up for it?
Looks like I don't
really have a choice,
given that the chief of Section
2 already gave his approval.
The Public Safety
official we're looking for
was last heard from in a
small town called Montalchino.
He'd been investigating an
assassin named Pinocchio
who works for the Padania,
better known to us as
the Five Republics Faction.
My advice to you is to
simply watch your ass.
You know I can go if
you don't feel up to it.
It might be too much
for a Section 2 pansy.
Thank you for the offer...
but it won't be necessary.
My Triela does exceptional work.
We'll be just fine.
If you feel that way and refuse
to increase her conditioning,
then it's your responsibility
to train her correctly.
Though to be perfectly honest,
I'm not one to talk.
I'm not gonna give
her conditioning
when she doesn't need it...
That's what's bothering me.
We're both stuck doing
jobs we're not good at.
Good morning, Hilshire!
How are you today?
Good morning, Triela...
You look ready.
So this is Montalcino.
It looks like every town
in the middle of Tuscany.
I feel really out of place here.
Uncomfortable.
We usually don't come to
the countryside, do we?
Are you sure about
these clothes...?
I feel like I'm
going to stand out.
No, they'll be useful to us...
For example...
What if I want to take you
out to a nice restaurant?
And besides...
Besides?
They look very nice on you.
So about this Public
Safety Official...
since his car is still
in the parking lot,
does that mean we
look for him in town?
And who is this Pinocchio
person he was looking for?
These are all good questions...
But let's start out by finding
the hotel Cohan was staying at.
I got one more...
Why are we the ones they sent
out here to track down this guy?
Beats me...
Section 2 isn't the most
respected division
at the agency.
So I guess this could be
some kind of conspiracy.
Oh well... Nothing
to worry about.
Understood...
We're always surrounded
by enemies, aren't we?
It doesn't bother me.
I have an ally I can
trust above all others.
Please don't say that
you're talking about me.
What if I am?
I promise I will never
betray you, Triela.
You can count on that.
Nicholas Cambio.
Here it is.
Cambio? I thought
the subject's name was Cohan?
Cambio is an alias
he's known to use.
Thank you...
I'd like to take a look inside
this room if you don't mind.
Why certainly, sir.
I'm impressed.
You're really good
at that stuff.
Well, thank you...
I was a police
detective at one point.
Comes naturally. This is my
real identity-only altered.
I'm still 99% cop, I just
work someplace else now.
By that logic, if you're 99%
cop, I must be a total fake.
Triela.
Open the suitcase.
Right.
Bust the locks if you have to.
I don't have to.
I've been practicing.
Must be an address
or a phone number.
I'm going downstairs
to check this out...
Yes, sir.
"The Adventures of Pinocchio."
Pinocchio was a puppet boy
made from magical firewood.
Every night, he would
sit by the window
and wish on the same
star for the same gift--
to repay Mister Geppetto
for creating him.
He tried to repay
him on his own,
but because his head
was made of wood,
it only got him into trouble.
One day, something
terrible happened
and Pinocchio was taken
away from Mister Geppetto.
He fought the whole
time to get back home
and faced many
adventures along the way.
Upon returning to
Geppetto's loving arms,
a blue fairy
granted him one wish
and Pinocchio was transformed
into a real, live boy.
What a stupid story.
Hello there!
I'm sorry. Do you live here?
Huh? No... But I
live kinda close by.
Are you... Are you
looking for Pino?
Actually, no.
I came to see
someone named Massimo.
Is this his house?
Massimo hasn't been here
for a really long time.
He lives in Milan now.
That's why he's renting
this place to Pino.
I think they're related.
Is that so...
What's that?
My mom made it.
I came by to bring some to Pino.
I see... It looks delicious.
Well, thank you...
You've been a big help.
I guess pretty girls can be
cool and easygoing, too...
It seems like someone else
is living in that house...
Like a relative or something.
She said his name was Pino.
I heard something
about a man renting
the second home of
a rich man here...
This definitely seems
to be the place
of the official
we're looking for.
I hope the microphone I planted
helps us learn something.
This is becoming too much
work for just the two of us.
It'll take about
an hour for help
from the Florence
branch to arrive.
Pino?
Freeze!
Drop the gun, now! Drop it!
A kid...? Are you one of
those government assassins?
A what...? But I...
Put the gun down...!
Leave it on the table!
--No! Please! Let me go!
--Who is this girl?
--I don't know what's going on!
--I don't know.
I figured she was
one of those assassins
you were talking about earlier.
Aurora...
Pino!
Do you know her?
Pino...! Help me...! Please!
What are you doing here?
I told you to stay away from me.
Why...?! Pino...!
I don't understand!
I told you not
to hang around me.
This is bad...
It sounds like
they've caught the girl.
Do you think the F.R.F.
might be holed up in that house?
Triela... Bust in
and save her...
Are you sure you want
me to do that now...?
Our back up hasn't
even arrived yet.
Plus, we don't know what
the Public Safety
Official's status is--
or how many we're up against.
I promise I won't say anything!
Let me go home! Please!
I can't just ignore her.
Triela! Get in there
and save that girl!
Right. I'm on my way!
Pinocchio! Explain to
us what's going on!
She's just a kid
from the neighborhood.
She follows me around.
Won't leave me alone.
What are you gonna do about it?
What do you mean...?
I have to kill her now...
She's seen your faces.
Hold on...!
It's not that big
of a deal, alright?
It is if it interferes
with my old man's work.
You know...
I'm the one who
chooses who we kill.
Have it your way...
You guys are really
nice, aren't you?
All right, let's get out of here
and report to Cristiano later...
Does that sound like
a good plan to you?
Freeze, Padania!
Drop your weapons and
get down on the floor!
It looks like this one
is the real assassin.
What was your first clue?
Get down...! All of you!
Franco...! Go on ahead!
Hold it right there!
I'm sorry about this.
I'll let you go soon, I promise.
Freeze...! Police!
Is there something wrong?
Now hand me your weapon.
Flanca.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Triela...! Triela!
Are you all right? Talk to me.
Hilshire...!
Take it easy...
You probably have a concussion.
Where's the girl?
She's safe.
We let the police
take care of her.
The Public Safety
Official's body
was found in the wine cellar.
I guess it was Pinocchio who
was staying there after all.
And the others?
I'm sorry... But
they all got away.
I can't believe I
let them escape...
without even a scratch.
You also saved a
little girl's life...
and we both made it out alive.
There's nothing to regret.
We had no idea who
we were dealing with...
Besides, I'm the one
who told you to storm--
I'm cybernetic! And I was
beaten with human hands!
Everything... all the risks...
Every sacrifice I've made
has been for nothing.
It was all meaningless.
Triela...
Please don't touch me!
I just want to be
alone for awhile.
How about the
vineyards in Frascati?
Considering what just happened,
I think we should head
south-closer to Rome.
Sounds good. I'll find
us a rental car...
And I'll call
Cristiano on the way.
Is your hand still
swollen? Let me see.
So...
That girl who came
in with the shotgun--
was she a government assassin?
I don't know. But I
was about to finish her off.
I just couldn't do it.
I'm really sorry that
you lost your pendant.
But no matter how many
memories it holds...
It isn't the object
itself that matters.
It's what's in your heart...
And you'll never lose that.