I won't be long.
Got it.
Fernando.
Jean?
Did you complete
your military service?
Why the hell are you here?!
How dare you come here and
show your face to my sister!
You get to live your cushy
life with no worries...
never stopping to
make the Padania pay!
Say something...
Anything, you bastard.
I'm sorry.
Your shirt...
Are you part of the
left-wing movement now?
That's a bad idea...
Getting into these politics...
It's more dangerous
than you think.
I'm gonna make them
pay for what they did...
I have to avenge my sister!
Why? Why, Jean...
I used to be so proud of you.
You're the one
guy I looked up to.
I couldn't wait for you
to marry my sister...
so we could finally be brothers.
Hey. What do you need?
I ran into Fernando.
No kidding. He came to
visit her grave too?
He was acting strangely...
I want you to tail him
when he leaves here.
Got it.
Hi, Sofia...
I want you to know that
over these past two years,
I've killed 56 Padania members.
And I promise you that
I will continue this fight,
until they're wiped off
the face of the earth.
Damn...
It's Fernando...
I'm heading back to
the apartment now...
One thing...
I'm going to need a gun.
Alright. He's on the move.
I'll continue to shadow him at
a distance and keep you posted.
Don't do anything
stupid, tough guy...
You don't wanna
throw your life away.
You're a cop?! Dammit!
All we got is that
he was planning
to attack
that apartment.
Not exactly sure why.
Whose place is it?
I asked around,
but didn't get much...
Some people said that a man
from Venice moved in recently.
The Venice Faction.
It could be, I suppose.
Doesn't surprise me--
Venice has been sending
a fair amount of
terrorists into Rome lately.
If nothing else,
I know that Fernando
is part of the
left-wing movement...
He probably heard about the
apartment from an associate.
I have no problem
making him talk.
But he's your old pal, so
I'd rather have your say so.
So what do we do...? Your call.
If a Padania member lives here,
we take care of him and we go.
Done. I'll get us ready.
Angelica...
And then Fernando...
What should we do about him?
We'll hand him over
to the local police
and have him cool
off for a week or two.
Must be frustrating.
But I know exactly how he feels.
Oh, yeah... I do too.
You ready, Angelica?
It's go time.
I'm ready, Marco.
Who is it?
It's the police. I have
some questions for you.
Don't move!
Jean...
Now... Make this
son-of-a-bitch talk.
I'll get started.
Rico?
You want to tell me just
what you're doing there?
Uh... I don't' know...
My... My hands are--
We have more work to do.
What is wrong?
You can't stand up?
Jean, Jean please!
I've no need for
someone who's useless.
Do you have everything
you need, Rico?
Yes... I sure do.
We'll take the car
all the way to Rome...
That should put us in
Venice by the afternoon.
I... have a question.
Yeah, what is it?
Why's your face hurt?
Don't worry about it.
It's nothing.
Yes, sir.
There's a large
wealth gap between
the north half of
Italy and the south.
Which is why we have
these rich northerners
doing everything they can to
turn Italy into a federal union.
These radical
nationalists are known as
the Five Republics Faction,
or FRF, due to its original
advocacy for splitting Italy
into five separate states.
Milan is in the north.
Rome in the middle...
And Naples in the south.
Toss in Sardinia...
toss in Sicily... there you go.
Alright...
Then where does the
Venice Faction come from?
The Milan Faction
wanted to separate
the entire northern region.
And the Venice Faction,
only wanted to liberate
the Veneto province.
Which caused a fair amount
of contention between them.
Sounds like a story
from the Renaissance.
He's a Padanian politician.
What's Padania?
The Milan Faction
once called itself
the Padania Republic Faction
and declared its independence.
So now Padania is
just another name used
for the Five Republics Faction.
Sounds like everyone has
plenty of enemies left around.
Yeah, but we're winning...
Especially after Milan.
But it's not over yet.
There are still a lot
of them out there.
Excuse me... Sorry about that.
It's fine.
Are you Jean from Rome?
Yes.
My name's Altmeyer.
I'm with the Venice Branch.
Thanks for coming.
So your name...
I'm guessing it's German?
Sure is... Yeah...
It makes things twice
as hard for me with
the Venice Faction
always sniffing around here.
So, what brings the two
of you here out of the blue?
We caught word that there are
some Padanian operatives here,
and we needed a good guide
to make sure we find them.
We're a branch office.
We focus on
information-gathering.
You're not gonna go raise
a lot of hell, are you?
We can handle the hell we raise.
There are a lot more
patrol boats these days.
Yeah.
Are they having
terrorism problems?
No, Rico...
Padania doesn't
bother wasting its time
attacking
sightseeing locations.
They're doing all this for
the tourists peace of mind.
Europe has a long history
of being politically unstable,
and they think this helps.
They're policemen
on military service.
Right.
They wear the uniform but
don't have decent training.
The only thing that those
clowns are really any good for
is a parade.
Um, I'm wondering...
How long until we
can get to work?
Don't rush it...
We're waiting until night fall.
Do you know the man
living at this address?
I do... He's a local Mafia boss.
Did you know he's sending
terrorists into Rome every day?
No, that one's new to me.
I can't say I'm knocked
over by surprise that
the local Mafia is in bed with
the Venice Faction, though.
What's the plan?
We go in and we either
capture him or kill him.
The two of you...?
But she's just a little girl!
Plus, his bodyguards are
former San Marco marines!
Those guys'll rip
you two to pieces!
She's not just a girl...
She is a most
invaluable tool to me.
I can't do it without her.
What is it?
Hey... What's up?
How're things going?
That's it, Jean sir... All done.
Whoa!
We should probably
get out of here
before more of
these guys show up.
Jean, look.
Looks like their PC
is still logged in.
We can use this to learn
more about their organization.
Tomorrow will be fun.
Yes, sir.
Wait a second...
You're not done?
After all this blood,
all these corpses, and that PC,
you're still not satisfied
with what you've got?
No.
Rico! Stop that damn
boat right now!
Kill them all if you have to!
Yes, sir!
No!
She's been hit!
Are you all right...?
Where did the bullet hit you?
So pretty...
I never knew you enjoyed
the sea, this much.
I do.
It's breathtaking...
so beautiful...
It always makes me so sad.
Especially at sunset.
Forget about it...
Just run along and play.
I'll be relaxing up here.
Okay.
Silly...