Caterina, you can't be serious.
You're really dropping
out of school?
Yeah. I turned in all
of the documents today.
It's just so sudden...
Why didn't you come and
talk to me about it first?
I'm sorry, Patricia...
But I've already decided.
Couldn't you just
take some time off?
I'm taking the
country to court...
I have to give it
everything I've got.
If it goes to trial,
do you think you can win?
My father's lawyer and
a few of his friends
are going to help me out.
I know... I won't lose.
So you never told me
how that whole thing
turned out with that
officer at the Pantheon.
Oh... Well, he keeps
asking me out all the time.
That's good...
So things are going better
than I thought, huh...
The guy seemed to be
so pushy at first,
I wasn't sure if
he was your type.
Come on. I have you
to thank, you know it.
If you hadn't been
with us at the movies,
I don't know if he
and I would've spoken.
He's nicer than you
thought he'd be, right?
Yeah.
Of course... I went through
all that trouble for you...
Don't screw it up now.
Sitting out there alone
again... He's weird.
Can't argue with that.
The three of us have been out
here for a solid month now...
And he still acts likes
he met us yesterday.
Too bad for him.
I assume he doesn't
value much in life
or feel anything
close to happiness.
I'm surprised to hear
that coming from you.
Well, it's about time
for me to hit the road...
You get the documents ready
for presentation, okay?
You going in to
Rome to see Nino?
Yeah... Thought I'd
check to see how he is.
I don't like this.
I can't imagine you would.
But someday... you'll get it.
How can you be so sure?
Flanca, what is it
you're fighting against?
Do you even know when
victory will be yours?
If you're in this to
avenge your old man...
Tell me how many people have
to die to set things right.
Think that over now,
while you still got the time.
Don't wait until you're
an old dog like me
who doesn't have it in him
to keep running anymore.
Nino. You were weak.
That was the problem.
Caterina. I'm so sorry
about your father.
I never thought he would have
been fated to die in prison.
Uncle Marinov, I have to ask...
Were the charges...
Were the charges
against my dad faked?
I'm not sure, but what I do
know is he wasn't a man to keep
connections to the
underworld like me.
There are too many
suspicious things
about the charges against
him to know for sure.
Tell me... What do
you intend to do now?
I won't give up.
It's been a long time...
Good to see you
again, Uncle Marinov.
You've grown up
well, my Caterina.
It must've been...
about eight years ago
when you declared you were
going to become an activist.
I didn't think you had it
in you, but here you are.
I need to know...
Were you ever able to find out
anything about your father?
I didn't... and that's
not what I focus on now.
So the path of truth has
given way to that of revenge.
I see.
I would assume you're working
with Cristiano of Milan now,
is that correct?
Yes.
Then you must be careful.
The northern isolationists
are fighting the government
in the open now, not to mention
their ongoing internal
struggles for power.
Don't get caught up in their
petty in-fighting, Caterina.
Hey Jeremiah, look at this.
The blonde woman there...
It's Flanca.
No way.
That's definitely her.
Same lady Special Ops
tusseled with in Montalchino.
From the wanted posters?
But why would she come
to see that broker, here?
Who cares? I'm gonna call it in.
Irma... It's Jeremiah.
Where are you right now?
Driving around the highway loop.
I'm over the near the airport.
At the stakeout, we've spotted
a wanted Padania agent.
Let's meet at the rendezvous...
be sure and bring Vito with you.
Got it.
So what's the deal?
What are we doin'?
What do you think
we're doin'...?
We're gonna catch her.
I don't teach anyone anymore.
I've given that crap up.
So just turn the hell
around and get out of here.
Franco, please...
There hasn't been a
greater bomb crafter
in our lifetime than
your grandfather!
I know he trained you to make
bombs the same way he did.
Listen, making bombs
wasn't quite the life plan
I had hoped for...
I just helped the old man
out when he needed it.
He died last month anyway.
So there's no reason to
continue down that road.
Now leave, would you? Before
it gets so dark that you can't.
You didn't listen to
a single word I said.
Those in this world
with great power
are obligated to put
those skills to work!
Power...?
Lady the last thing
I have is any power.
All anyone wants
or needs these days
are simple bombs that they
can detonate by cell phone.
My grandfather...
He devoted himself entirely to
the art of the handcrafted bomb.
Which today, most people
would call antiquated.
Who told you about me?
Someone close... Angelo Marinov.
Marinov, huh...?
Then you must've
been turned down
by plenty of others
before you came to me.
That's the way
things work, right?
You get a list and
you start at the top,
then work your way down.
And it doesn't matter
what list it is,
usually, I'm the guy
near the bottom.
So what game are
you playing here?
What kind of a plan does a green
killer like you have stewing.
My father was convicted on
false charges and imprisoned.
I took the case to court, but
he died before we could try it.
You want revenge?
I want to change
an unjust world!
That's nice. Then find
Jesus and preach the word.
Keep your hands off me...
You don't have all he
answers to everything,
you drunk son of a bitch!
How would you know anything
sitting around here
smashed all day?!
Stop! Please!
Oh, thank you! It's my
wife! She's needs help!
Can you help us?!
What's wrong?!
We were on our way
to the hospital
and the car just
stopped running!
This looks bad.
Help me get her into my car.
Don't move!
Hey, what's going on?
I'm going to pick up Flanca.
Did something happen?
The tracker on the car says
its sitting off the highway
and hasn't moved.
Is she in danger?
Probably.
It's her, alright.
Flanca of the Padania.
That's a big fish...
One of us should inform the
chief when we leave here.
Calm down, don't be
in such a rush...
We haul her back to
headquarters and
Public Safety's gonna yank
her right out from under us.
We should have her talk
while we have the opportunity.
Do whatever you want...
Me... I'm gonna go file
a report... Matthias!
Right... Her stuff.
Yeah, gather all her things
and take it upstairs.
Of course.
Say, Irma. You absolutely
sure about this?
About what?
'Bout Jeremiah...
I gotta admit, I'm a little
worried that he might kill her.
Have faith in your associates.
Look, It was for your sake
that he... uh, no, nothing.
Let's let him
unwind a bit, okay?
Keep it up... I have
nothing to tell you!
That's gonna work just fine
'cuz I have nothing to ask you.
Look... you bitch...
I only want to make you hurt.
So you're telling me the
pregnant girl in the car
was just a ruse...?
Thank goodn--
Her name is Irma!
And she almost died
three years ago
in an explosion you designed.
She still has a boatload of
shrapnel swimming around
in her stomach, thanks to you!
While I'm on the subject,
you should know that
that same bombing took my left
eye and two of my fingers!
Tell me... How does that feel?!
I asked you how does that feel!
Every person in the world
carries around some
kind of hatred.
If you think being hurt makes
you special, I'm sorry...
you're gravely mistaken.
Matthias!
You...? His student...? Come on.
Your names Nino, isn't it?
So Nino, just what's so funny?
It's damn near impossible
to believe Franco
can teach a woman anything!
Don't you think so, bro?
And anyway, I thought you quit
the bomb-making
business again, Franco?
Something must've
stirred you up...
Love at first sight?
It's nothing like that.
Let's go, Franco. C'mon.
Calm down, Miss... Miss...
What was your name?
Call her Flanca.
What is that?
Some kind of alias?
'Cuz it's a masterpiece!
Franco...
Good, you're conscious...
Hold still.
Are you badly hurt?
Uh... No...
Bastard.
How do you think I'm
feeling now, you prick?
Oh, no. It's Irma.
Too late. She's dead.
Damn Padania...
No, wait!
Not good!
Henrietta! Can you stand?!
Thank you... You saved
everyone's lives, you know?
Great.
That's a pretty screwed up
thing using a body as a bomb...
I bet they get off on this
stuff... The bastards...
Are you alright?
Hilshire, get up!
Are you hurt?
No, I'll be fine.
Triela, you're bleeding!
It's just a scratch...
I can have it stitched up.
Hilshire! You guys get hit?!
We're fine. Just a couple nicks.
It was him... He was here...
You ran into some
real trouble out there.
Don't worry. They'll get
what's coming to them.
Franco.
Thank you... Thanks
for coming to get me.
Maybe now you've
learned your lesson
not to run off on
your own anymore.
I did... I think I'll be
taking it easy for a while.
At least until we
blow the bridge.
Where are you going?
Out in the hall.
Pinocchio... I owe you
a thanks, as well...
You came through today
with flying colors.
Well... Yeah... I guess
I did, so you're welcome.
Pinocchio...
Uncle, hi! What are
you doing here?!
Marinov let me know
about the recent debacle...
I came here to see
how Flanca was doing.
She's right through
here, isn't she?
--Yes.
--Good.
I heard about your hesitation
to kill in Montalcino.
That was because...
A hired killer is done for...
when he hesitates even one time.
Forget about that...
I also heard that you saved
Flanca's life today, right?
Well done.
Thank you... Uncle.