We'll return the day after
tomorrow for your decision.
I hope, for your sake,
it's the right one, Sebas.
Going out for a bit?
[BRAIN]
Yeah.
[GAZEF]
Got any money?
No, but if I need to,
I can sell an item--
Go crazy.
Thanks, Gazef. I'll try
not to spend it all.
[inhales, sighs]
[gasps]
Virgin! Lookin' for us?
[CLIMB] It's been
too long, Lady Gagaran.
[growls]
[CLIMB]
I-I mean, "Miss" Gagaran.
Better.
[CLIMB]
And you, Lady Evileye.
Guess it has been
a while. What's up?
You here to get lucky
with me, virgin?
No, nothing like that.
Lady Aindra is currently
visiting with Princess Renner.
She asked to give you a message.
Yeah? Well, spit it out then.
Right.
"We're going into
action on the double.
Be ready at a moment's notice.
We are going to hit
them where it hurts."
End message.
Is that all?
Seems like such a minor chore
for the Princess' bodyguard.
Nah. Oh, yeah!
Gazef came by earlier.
He gave me a private
lesson in swordsmanship.
Crazy, huh?
And I used the strike
you taught me!
He was so impressed that
he even complimented it!
You're kidding--he liked it?
Sounds like you're movin'
up in the world, kid.
Even so...
[CLIMB]
I know. I won't grow complacent.
I'll devote myself
to further training.
That's good and all, but listen.
That move could be
countered pretty easily.
It's time you
came up with a move
you could transition into.
Whoa.
Lord Stronoff told me
the same thing earlier!
Great minds.
Come to think of it,
you wanted somethin'
from Evileye, too, right?
Well, go ahead and ask her.
Well...
[EVILEYE]
No. Magic is beyond your reach.
Stick to the sword.
[EVILEYE sighs]
You don't seem very convinced.
Those with talent possess
it from the outset.
Take Gazef Stronoff,
he's a good example.
Can you catch up to where
he is on effort alone?
[EVILEYE]
I'm not saying give up.
Just know what
you're up against.
[EVILEYE]
Foolish. Utterly foolish.
Those who chase after
the unobtainable
are certain to ruin themselves.
I'm well aware of that.
[EVILEYE]
You're bound for an early grave.
Think of the people
who will weep for you
should you continue.
I never thought I'd see the day.
The imp's worried
about you, Climb!
Isn't that sweet?
[EVILEYE] Keep your
voice down, muscle head!
Well, it's true, isn't it?
[EVILEYE]
Ugh.
First, gain some
magic knowledge.
Once you increase
your knowledge,
you'll be able to tell what your
magic-using opponents are after.
Then you can take the
appropriate action.
End of lesson.
Thanks.
[EVILEYE] Climb, don't do
anything to lose your humanity.
Power isn't worth it.
Right.
[EVILEYE]
Look, I get it.
When it comes
to natural ability,
humans drew the short straw
compared to other races.
In fact, many of the
legendary Thirteen Heroes
were species other than human.
Like Black Knight,
the former owner
of the cursed sword Kilineiram
now wielded by our leader.
He had demonic blood
running through his veins.
Huh. I keep
forgettin' about that.
Tell me.
Is it true, at full power,
it has enough dark energy
to swallow a nation whole,
or is that a fat
sack of horse crap?
[EVILEYE]
Where did you hear that?
I overheard Lakyus
talkin' to herself
a few nights back.
[LAKYUS] Only evil unbound
could create a dark sword
of such terrible power.
Even though I am in
the service of the gods,
keeping it restrained...
takes all that I have!
[EVILEYE]
Hm.
Then, another time...
[LAKYUS laughs] Don't
underestimate my dark power,
for it is rooted
in the purest black!
I will dominate your
flesh and unleash
my curse upon the world!
[LAKYUS grunts] Your power is
at its strongest tonight,
that's for sure.
But I will not let
you do as you wish.
I swear it!
Please, Ring of
the Holy Valkyrie,
lend me your protection!
Hey! Lakyus!
[gasps]
I'm fine; there's nothing
to see here! Honest!
[EVILEYE] Hm. As a priestess,
I guess she was embarrassed
being seen struggling
with a cursed item.
And it sounds like
those pointless-looking
armor rings weren't
just for fashion's sake.
Is Renner in danger?
C'mon, let's head to the palace!
[EVILEYE]
Don't panic!
There's nothing we can do
about this right now.
Even if we tried,
the only thing that can
stop an adamantite
is another adamantite.
[EVILEYE]
Yeah.
Oh. That reminds me.
I hear a third adamantite
class adventure team
recently sprung up in E-rantel.
Huh. That's news to me.
Who are they?
[EVILEYE] As I recall,
they're a team of two.
Their leader is Momon,
a warrior known as
the Raven Black Hero, and Nabe,
a powerful magic caster.
What? Just two of 'em?
The hell have they done
to earn adamantite class?
[EVILEYE] Well, they resolved
an incident in E-rantel
involving thousands of undead.
Then, they exterminated
the Goblin Tribal Coalition
headed northward.
Retrieved ultra-rare
medicinal herbs
from the Great Forest of Tob.
Slayed a giant basilisk.
And, as I understand it,
defeated a vampire
possessing tremendous
magical power.
Single-handedly.
Lastly, they subdued the
Wise King of the Forest
with their power and are
keeping him as a pet.
Holy hell.
These two sound awesome!
You mean...
Something like that would be
hard for you, Miss Gagaran?
I could handle
thousands of undead,
no problem, but a giant basilisk
with its petrifying
gaze and toxic venom?
No way.
Without restorative measures,
it'd be too much for me.
They are the ultimate
test for any warrior.
I know how strong Blue Rose is.
No, Miss Gagaran, there's no way
these newbies could best you!
Ha! Thanks for the praise,
kid! Let's get nasty.
I'll have to decline.
Better loosen up, or you'll
always be a virgin.
[EVILEYE]
Enough. Let's get moving.
Lakyus is expecting
us to be ready,
and I don't intend
to disappoint her.
As you wish.
[GAGARAN]
Climb.
Yes?
That sword around your hip--
it's not your usual weapon.
No, this is just a backup sword.
There's no tellin'
what might happen.
Always keep your
main weapon handy.
Also, do you have the
items I gave to you?
You mean those bells.
I have them right here.
[GAGARAN] Good. Keep three
healing potions on you,
just in case we need 'em.
Understood.
[EVILEYE] You'll make a
fantastic mother someday.
[GAGARAN]
Screw you, shorty.
[HORSE whinnies]
[CROWD murmuring]
[MAN 8A]
Punk-ass brat! You're filthy!
[grunts]
All he did was bump into him.
They'll kill the poor
kid at this rate.
[sighs]
What the hell?
Am I seeing things?
[MAN 8A] What're you tryin'
to pull, old timer?
[MAN 8C] Back off, if you
know what's good for you!
Let me through, please.
[gasps]
What? Ya deaf or stupid?
[SEBAS]
I'll say this once. Depart.
Make me!
--[MAN 8A grunts]
--[CROWD gasps]
[gasps]
Do not make me repeat myself.
[MEN yelping]
[MAN 8C]
We're sorry, sir!
[CLIMB]
Hey! Are you all right?
Thank goodness.
He's still breathing.
I've got a potion.
Here, try to swallow this.
Slowly. That's it. Good job.
You're gonna be
just fine, kiddo.
Thanks.
Sir?
[CLIMB panting]
Excuse me!
Is there something
you need, boy?
[panting]
Why'd you follow me, young man?
Sorry, that was
pretty rude of me.
My name's Climb. I'm a soldier.
I should've been there
to protect that kid
from those wretches.
Thanks for doing my job.
[SEBAS]
It was no bother.
Now, I must be going.
Wait a minute!
If you wouldn't mind, sir.
I'd like for you to teach me
the move you used back there.
What purpose would that serve?
[CLIMB]
I'm trying to improve myself.
To become stronger.
And after seeing your
outstanding technique,
I knew that learning even a
little of it would do just that.
[SEBAS]
All right. Show me your hands.
Sure.
They seem strong and firm.
The perfect hands for a warrior.
No. I'm afraid my swordsmanship
is negligible at best.
I think you grossly
underestimate your abilities.
Now then, may I take a
closer look at your weapon?
Of course.
I see.
This isn't your usual sword.
How did you discern that?
[SEBAS] The number of
blemishes in the blade.
Sorry you had to see that.
I was neglectful.
Quite all right.
Besides, now I understand
the type of person you are.
The hands and weapon are mirrors
which reflect the warrior
who wields them.
You present an extremely
favorable impression.
Thanks.
[SEBAS] One last thing--
please be honest.
For what reason do you aspire
to improve yourself?
Your desire spurred
you to chase me
and request my guidance.
While my initial
impression is that
you are a trustworthy sort.
I do wanna know why you're
seeking greater power.
Well, you see...
Because I'm a man.
Indeed. Based on your answer,
I have decided the type
of training you'll receive.
Thank you, sir!
However, before we begin,
you should know
that I don't think
you have talent.
I'll be frank.
There's a chance
you'll die from this.
[SEBAS] It depends entirely
on the strength of your heart.
If there's someone
truly precious to you,
think of them,
and you'll be fine.
Then, I am ready.
Please proceed.
You're confident you
won't die, then?
Very well, young Climb.
We'll start your
training immediately.
What, you mean right
here in the alley?
Draw your weapon and
stand ready, please.
[CLIMB]
Right!
Hold fast to your wits, Climb.
Few have seen this,
and even fewer survived.
[gasps]
[SEBAS] I hope this isn't
the extent of your manhood.
How will you fare when
I actually strike?
[CLIMB grunts]
I suppose you'll join the dead.
[SEBAS grunts]
[CLIMB grunts]
[pants]
Congratulations, you've passed.
How does it feel
to have overcome
the fear of death at your age?
[gasps]
You did well to avoid
dying of shock.
It happens sometimes.
Or a person will be prepared
to die and, as a result,
abandon their hold on life.
Um. I...
I have to ask. Who are you?
What is it you do?
If you don't mind, that is.
I am simply an old man who knows
how to handle himself,
young Climb.
Nothing more.
[SEBAS]
Now, once again--
[BRAIN]
Wait a second!
[panting]
[CLIMB]
An acquaintance of yours?
[SEBAS]
No.
I assume, he is not a friend
of yours, either, then?
[BRAIN] Sorry. Didn't
mean to startle you.
I'm a fighter.
Name's Brain Unglaus.
[CLIMB gasps]
Again, I apologize
for my interruption.
But I had to sate my curiosity.
I know your name.
You once went toe-to-toe
with Lord Stronoff
and nearly came out on top.
All right, ask whatever
you need to know.
Wait, you meant me?
Before.
How could you just stand
there and face death
without hesitation?
Uh.
I need to know.
Tell me.
That was far beyond what any
normal man could withstand.
Even I--or rather,
someone like me--
could never bear such terror.
But not you.
You held your ground.
Fought through it.
I need to know how.
Come on, I'm begging here.
Not sure, honestly.
However, it might be because
I was thinking about
my mistress the entire time.
--Your what?
--Mistress.
I don't know how, but thinking
about her made it bearable.
It helped me through.
That's all it was?
[SEBAS]
Lord Unglaus.
Young Climb's steadfast
loyalty to the lady he serves
allowed him to persevere.
When people have someone
that is important to them,
you'd be amazed at
the incredible power
they can muster.
That, more than any muscle,
is the true measure
of a person's strength.
Find something you refuse
to lose, and you, too,
can demonstrate a power greater
than you ever thought possible.
I've already forsaken everything
that was important to me.
[CLIMB]
That's fine!
I was able to do it,
and I have no talent.
It'll be no sweat for
someone of your caliber!
Strong and kind to boot.
You're gonna go far, kid.
Thanks a lot. I really
have been a fool.
If I may, Lord Unglaus.
You can drop the
"Lord" business.
Believe me, I'm nobody
a person such as yourself
needs to pay respect to.
In that case,
you may call me Sebas.
That would please me greatly.
Now then, as I was saying.
I think it would be best
if you and young Climb
left here as
quickly as possible.
It appears I have some visitors.
Whoa.
Over there, as well.
They look like they
mean business.
Poisoned blades.
Careful. I think
they're assassins.
Hopefully, I won't
get in the way,
but I can't let you
fight them alone.
I swore to protect
the peace in this city.
I refuse to go back
on that oath.
Well, damn.
Guess I'll join in
the fun as well.
[SEBAS]
In that case, I will take care
of the three reprobates
flanking us.
Please deal with the pair
in front, if you wouldn't mind.
[BOTH]
Right.
This is not your lucky day.
I'm afraid I'll be your partner
for this dance of death.
[ASSASSINS gasp]
I'd appreciate it
if you'd focus your
attention on me.
Whoa. Did you see that?
Yeah.
If someone claimed Lord Sebas
was the strongest man
in the kingdom,
I'd agree with 'em.
Even stronger than
Lord Stronoff?
Gazef and I together
wouldn't stand
a chance in hell against him.
Now. Here they come.
I'll take the one on the left.
The right's all yours.
[BRAIN]
Hey there.
I hate to ask,
but would you mind
being my training
dummy for a bit?
I'm a bit rusty.
Oh-ho. So, that's
what the story is.
[ASSASSINS yell]
You're out of practice.
Then this might be
exactly what you needed.
Opponents like this are perfect
for shaking off the rust.
[CLIMB grunts]
Don't get in deep till
you've determined his reach!
Right!
He strikes me as a man
of great character.
[CLIMB grunts]
[yelps]
Fear is an important
emotion, for sure.
But you can't let
yourself be bound by it.
If your physical abilities
aren't up to the task,
prevail with your heart.
And never forget that your mind
is the sharpest weapon
in your arsenal.
My lord.
If I fall here, tell Renner--
Please tell Her Highness
I fought like a
warrior till the end.
[yells]
Here we go. Martial Art, Slash!
[ASSASSIN 8D groans]
Well done, Climb.
Not too shabby. For a kid.
They must've been following me
since I left the mansion.
I think it's fair to say they're
in the employ of Succulent.
What did you do to him?
It's a skill that's called
"Palm of the Puppeteer,"
and it appears to be working.
Now then, to interrogate him.
[BRAIN] Eight Fingers
is a relatively large
criminal society within
the kingdom, right?
[CLIMB]
It is.
Succulent's name has
come up a few times as well.
Apparently he's one
of the "Six Arms."
He's an adamantite.
I'm guessing you don't plan
to take this lying down, Sebas?
They've left me little
choice, haven't they?
The first thing I'll
do is bring down
the source of all this trouble.
Succulent will be there, too.
Best to stamp out any sparks,
before they start
a raging inferno.
I'd be grateful if you
would carry this lot
to the nearest guardhouse.
I can't back out.
I'd like to offer my sword to
the cause, if you'll have it.
And that goes for me, as well.
Unglaus has the experience
and skill to survive this,
but you might find yourself
in a bit of peril, young Climb.
If I ran away because of danger,
it would only prove
that I am unfit
to serve my mistress or country.
You're resolved to see this
through to the end, then?
[CLIMB]
Yes.
In that case, gentlemen,
there is nothing more
to be said on the matter.
I accept your support.
Prepare to do battle.
[BOTH]
Right.
[AINS] Sebas decides to
confront the establishment
that imprisoned Tuare,
one, as it happens,
that is owned by Eight Fingers
and currently protected
by Succulent of Six Arms.
[AINS]
Along with Brain and Climb,
who volunteered their aide,
Sebas prepares to climb
into a nest of vipers.
[AINS] Chapter Nine:
"Soaring sparks of fire."
What are the thoughts of men,
when faced with death?