[DEMIURGE gasps]
[AINS] Evening. So which
one of you will be my foe?
[EVILEYE]
Raven Black Hero!
I am Evileye of Blue Rose!
We should form a party.
Two adamantite adventurers
might be able to take him down!
[EVILEYE gasps]
[EVILEYE] No. I'd just
be wasting his life, too.
I can't ask him to do that.
[AINS]
Understood.
[EVILEYE gasps]
[DEMIURGE]
Before we begin,
may I have your name, warrior?
You may call me Jaldabaoth.
[AINS]
That's quite a mouth-full.
Fine. I'll play along.
I am Momon. Adamantite
class adventurer.
What is your purpose here?
[DEMIURGE] Apparently, an item
with the power to summon
and subjugate my kind has
found its way into the city.
I would prefer it not
remain in the wrong hands,
you understand.
[EVILEYE]
He got information out of him
without even trying.
He's a first-rate
adventurer, all right.
[AINS]
Demiur--
Jaldabaoth, is there
truly no option
but to oppose each other?
[DEMIURGE]
No, there is not.
[AINS] Very well.
That keeps my job simple.
I just have to defeat you.
[AINS]
That's not a problem, right?
[DEMIURGE]
I'll have to resist.
But, I'm sure you knew that.
[AINS]
Here goes!
[AINS grunts]
[DEMIURGE grunts]
[EVILEYE] What is this
feeling? It can't be...
How?
My heart stopped beating
a long time ago.
[EVILEYE]
Lord Momon. You're amazing!
[CLIMB]
We need to move.
Come. This way.
You feeling all right?
Okay, let's leave
while Lord Sebas
has them distracted.
Is something wrong?
You're staring.
Huh? Oh, no. It's nothing.
[LOCKMEYER]
Let's go.
[gasps, grunts]
[CLIMB gasps]
[gasps] Zero?
So, you know me. I'm flattered.
[ZERO]
I never forget a face.
You're Brain Unglaus, aren'tcha?
If you're here,
I guess Succulent
wasn't full of crap after all.
He was outmatched.
In recognition of your
extraordinary talent,
I'll offer you one chance
to walk out of here.
Prostrate before me,
and swear your undying
loyalty to Six Arms.
And kill the kid
for good measure.
Heh.
I thought that'd be the case.
Hold it.
I expect this fight
to be one on one.
Lockmeyer, you and Climb
take care of her.
You've got it.
[SUCCULENT] Nothing gets
past you, does it?
Well, moving behind
me once my back
was turned was kind of
a dead giveaway, genius.
'Course, I suspected
you were a rat
the moment we found you.
Fine. We get it,
you've got sharp senses.
Succulent, kill these
small-timers for me,
and try not to screw it up.
Right. Good as dead. No prob.
[SUCCULENT]
Fancy meeting you here.
[SUCCULENT laughs]
[yells]
Well, I'll be damned.
Always thought the whole
"iron fisted" monk thing
was just big talk
for the ladies,
but you took it literally.
[panting]
[LOCKMEYER]
Don't be so stressed.
You've got a master thief
watching your back.
Poison?
Just your garden variety
Powder of Will 'o Wisp!
Thanks, Lockmeyer!
[CLIMB yells]
[SUCCULENT coughs]
Martial Art! Ability Release!
[gasps]
[SUCCULENT sputters]
[ZERO growling]
Dammit. That useless oaf.
You certainly live up
to your reputation.
I actually have to try a little.
In fact, this may be
the first time someone
was still standing
after this long.
Not bad yourself.
I guess we could start
fighting like we mean it.
Just for a bit.
[gasps]
[BRAIN]
Sounds good to me.
That thing your doing
is a sword barrier, right?
If I'm careless and step
too close, I'm done for.
Not bad.
Sadly, you can only
use the technique
when standing still
and on the defensive.
It's adorable, really.
Don't tell me that's
your ace in the hole.
Only one's survived it.
It's a slash attack
that uses both Field,
which never misses,
and my own special
blade attack, God Flash.
I call it Whistling Wind.
Fascinating.
Bet I could punch through
it and not break a sweat.
What do ya say, Brain?
Shall we put that to the test?
[SEBAS] So, this is where
you've been hiding.
Huh? How are you alive?
The others could have
ripped you apart
a dozen times by now.
Your colleagues are lying
in pools of their own blood,
feeding the crows.
You beat them and made it
here without a scratch?
Yeah, like I'd believe that.
The truth is often
seen as impossible.
Especially by the foolish.
Ah!
Lord Sebas!
The Tuare that was in
the basement was a fake.
We have to save her quick!
I appreciate your
concern, young Climb,
however, she's fine.
You can see for yourself.
Tuare. Please, wait here.
I'll just be a moment.
Okay.
[ZERO]
Time out, Unglaus.
I gotta send grandpa
here to the undertaker.
[ZERO] You just couldn't
leave well enough alone,
could you, old man?
You'll wish you had.
The true terror of
Six Arms is upon you.
Come, Panther!
Falcon! Rhinoceros!
Buffalo! And Lion!
[yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
You can't be human.
How the hell did you do that?
[SEBAS]
That was certainly a close one.
But, as fortune would have it,
I was a tad stronger than
the oversized brute.
[DEMIURGE] Aspect of the
Devil! Tentacle Wings!
[EVILEYE grunts]
[EVILEYE]
Huh?
[AINS]
Good. You weren't hurt.
[EVILEYE]
Uh... Yeah.
[EVILEYE gasps] On your
shoulder! Are you all right?
[AINS] Something this
minor is no issue.
Don't worry about me.
I'm just glad you're safe.
[EVILEYE]
Uh...
[EVILEYE chuckles nervously]
[DEMIURGE]
Bravo!
I'm honestly shocked
you could keep her alive.
It's not often I feel the
need to praise my opponent.
Well done.
[AINS]
You talk too much.
[EVILEYE gasps]
My Lord Momon!
[EVILEYE]
Forgive me, bards of the world!
Knights really do fight
to defend their maidens!
I should have never doubted you!
[EVILEYE] I feel more like
baggage than a princess.
Knock it off!
This isn't the time
for silly daydreams!
[DEMIURGE] Well. I believe
I'll be on my way.
[EVILEYE]
Huh?
[DEMIURGE] I must find the
item by any means necessary.
A circle of hell fire will soon
cover a section of the city.
Should you foolishly
choose to enter,
I promise you a slow and painful
journey into the afterlife.
Farewell.
[EVILEYE]
Huh? He's getting away!
We have to stop him.
[AINS]
We can't.
If we go after him,
he'll start fighting
like he really means it,
and if that happens...
[EVILEYE] Oh. Still protecting
me. You truly are gallant.
[MOMONGA] Great, what am
I going to do now?
[EVILEYE] After that, we managed
to drive the insect maid
right down to the ground.
[AINS]
Is that right?
[EVILEYE]
Huh?
[AINS]
Did you kill her?
[EVILEYE]
No, unfortunately.
Jaldabaoth made sure
that didn't happen.
[AINS]
I see.
Don't be hard on yours--
[NARBERAL growling]
[AINS]
Uh--
[AINS clears throat]
So, it could be that
Jaldabaoth only attacked you
to defend the insect maid.
Would you say
that's a possibility?
[EVILEYE] I'd say we tugged on
the tiger's tail, and got bit.
[EVILEYE]
But, you heard what he said.
Trapping part of the
city in hellfire?
No way that's just retaliation.
He would have done it even if
his servant wasn't attacked.
My friends were right
to challenge her.
I'm sure any of us would
have done the same.
[AINS] U-Uh. Of course,
without question.
I did not intend to blame
them for their fate.
I beg your pardon.
[EVILEYE]
Oh! No, no, please.
Lift your head.
A man as handsome
as you shouldn't be--
[EVILEYE squeals]
[EVILEYE]
Handsome? What am I saying?
I just can't help
myself around him.
It's been a few hundred years
since my last crush,
but there's nothing wrong
with that, is there?
Of course not!
He's everything I like,
and stronger to boot!
[AINS]
Miss Evileye?
[EVILEYE]
Ah! Yes! Hi. Lord Momon.
[AINS] I need to fill
Nabe in on a few things.
Excuse me a moment.
[EVILEYE]
Oh.
[AINS] She won't be
able to hear us here.
Nonetheless, we should
still be cautious
while we're around her.
Now then, Narberal.
[AINS]
I can pretty well guess
what Demiurge's
plan is, overall.
However, the more
precise a machine is,
the easier it is to disrupt.
One slip up could throw
a wrench into the gears.
We must prevent the
slightest misunderstanding
from knocking us
back to square one.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Indeed, I do.
I expected no less
from you, Lord.
[AINS]
I have everything well in hand.
[MOMONGA]
Who am I kidding?
The only reason I'm out here
is because some noble
named Raeven made a special
request of the guild.
We had to ride on
a Floating Board.
I felt like luggage
the whole time,
but the reward was
exceptional, so we managed.
And, once I saw
the disturbances,
I thought "Wait!
This is Momon's first big
fight in the capital city!
I gotta make a badass entrance!"
So I jumped.
[MOMONGA sighs] How did
things turn out this way?
[AINS]
Hm?
[AINS] Now, I need you to
get in touch with Demiurge.
I'd do it myself, but I can't
cast spells in this form.
Besides. If she saw me,
it would complicate things.
Hm... Is she staring?
She must have her
doubts about me.
Perhaps, but I don't
think that's the case.
Behind that mask of hers,
I think you'd find eyes filled
with lust and sparkles.
[AINS]
Let's not wax poetic.
I can read her thoughts
like the back of my hand.
There's no attraction.
Getting upset when
she spoke of Entoma
may have compromised us,
if only a little.
[gasps] I should have
expected as much.
Forgive me, Lord Ains.
Truly, your vision befits one
who sits upon the throne.
[AINS] Please, enough
with the flattery.
It was an obvious consideration
that arose from my own slip up.
Let's get the ball
rolling, Narberal.
Lord. Send Message.
[MOMONGA] Well, that should
keep my reputation as leader
from falling apart,
at least. Now then...
[MOMONGA] You know, it's hard
to believe that a little child
like her possesses
adamantite class strength.
[AINS]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Would you like me to
help you carry them?
[EVILEYE]
No need.
My friends should
be along shortly.
It's possible we'll
be able to cast
resurrection magic on them here.
I'd rather not move them.
[AINS]
Hm. You have a party member
who can cast resurrection magic?
[EVILEYE]
Uh, that's right.
Our team leader, Lakyus,
can invoke Raise Dead.
It's a fifth-tier spell.
Impressive, I guess.
[AINS]
And, your friends.
Will they be able to engage
in combat soon after?
[EVILEYE]
Mm-mm. I'm afraid not.
This magic costs a huge
amount of life force
at the time of resurrection.
Quite a toll.
[AINS]
I see.
[EVILEYE] As such, they won't
be able to move around
on their own for
a while afterwards.
I wouldn't even suggest it
for someone weaker than them.
They'd be reduced to ashes.
[AINS]
Unfortunate.
If you wouldn't mind,
could we wait here with you?
I would like to meet
this leader of yours.
Lady Lakyus.
[EVILEYE gasps]
Why do you want to meet, Lakyus?
[MOMONGA] Sure enough.
She's got her guard up.
[AINS] I would simply like
to meet the leader of Blue Rose.
She's a fellow adventurer,
and my senior in experience.
Is there some reason
why I shouldn't?
[EVILEYE]
No, no! No problem.
Not in the slightest.
[NARBERAL] Momon, sir! I think
you will want to see this.
[EVILEYE gasps]
[CLIMB] What will you do
after this, Lord Sebas?
I'll be taking Tuare
to a safe location.
I won't let this happen
to her ever again.
I understand.
Just so you know,
everything you've done
means the world to us.
Please, think nothing of it.
You have helped me keep
my promise to Tuare.
I will repay you, someday.
[CLIMB gasps]
Tell me I'm not the
only one seeing this.
[EVILEYE]
What is that?
[AINS]
The flames of Gehenna?
Good and brave adventurers.
Thank you for coming
together so quickly.
We face a dire crisis.
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
[RENNER]
Early this morning,
a wall of flame sprang
up around this area.
Cutting off a section
of the city.
However, these flames
are similar to an illusion,
and seem to cause
no harm upon contact.
Miss Lakyus, leader of
the famous Blue Rose,
confirmed this for us.
[LAKYUS]
I touched it with my own hand.
It didn't feel hot to the touch,
and I passed clear to the
other side without any issue.
However, there appears
to be a horde
of low-level demons
infesting the area.
The ringleader has identified
himself as Jaldabaoth.
He's an extremely fiendish
and powerful demon,
and many evil creatures of
power are serving under him.
How strong are we talking?
Two of the members of Blue Rose,
the warrior Gagaran, and the
thief Tia, were killed.
[EVILEYE] And he did it
with just one blow.
[ADVENTURERS gasp, murmur]
[EVILEYE]
Calm yourselves!
Yes, Jaldabaoth's
strength is immense.
I confronted him myself
and was powerless
against his might.
But we have someone
even stronger!
[EVILEYE]
The Raven Black Hero, Momon!
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
Fear not.
I know it seems hopeless,
but I wouldn't do this unless
I thought we could win.
I've devised a plan of attack
that I believe will succeed...
[RENNER] Lastly, we'll
need a detached force
of adventurers to rescue the
civilians currently trapped
within the flame wall.
If the demons are, indeed,
holding them captive,
they're probably using one
of the warehouse districts.
And have likely
split up families
to discourage dissent.
You'll go. Won't you, Climb?
Without hesitation.
Even if I die trying.
[BRAIN] Princess, would it
be okay if I tag along?
[RENNER]
You would be most welcome,
Lord Brain Unglaus.
[ADVENTURERS murmur]
Count me in. Sounds fun.
Thanks, everyone.
I shall remain here,
and pray to the gods
that every one of you
returns to us safely.
May the light shine upon you.
Happy hunting!
[ADVENTURERS cheer]
[ADVENTURERS]
Long live the Golden Princess!
[GAZEF]
Climb.
Take this with you.
What is it?
Looks like a magic item.
It is.
That ring can
transcend human bounds,
and push your strength
well past your limits.
[CLIMB]
Past my limits?
I can't possible accept
such a precious item!
You can.
The woman I got it from
trusts my judgment.
Bring it back to me.
[gasps]
[BRAIN]
We all have to come back.
For Princess Renner's sake.
[CLIMB]
Right!
[ZANAC] So you'll form a line
using the adventurers,
and back them up with the
guardsman in an effort
to thin out the
enemy's formation.
Heh. At that point,
the Raven Black Hero Momon,
and the Lady Nabe, along with
Lady Evileye of Blue Rose,
will break through the center
like a spear through fodder.
--Nice.
--[RAEVEN] But,
isn't Climb's mission
a bit too risky?
[RENNER] He'll be making
rounds inside the capital
along with your soldiers.
It's no different
than his usual duties.
[RENNER]
Yes, Climb may end up dying.
Then, my dear friend, Lakyus,
will cast her resurrection
magic on him.
And when his life force
has been weakened
by such a potent spell.
I will personally take
him into my tender care.
Since it was my order
that got him killed
to begin with, no one
would dare object.
I would only be
doing what's right.
So that's your game.
I suppose this was your plan
all along, dear sister?
[RENNER]
Yes.
[BOTH gasp]
[AINS] A part of the
royal capital has been
sectioned off by
a wall of flame,
turning the area within it
into a demon-filled hell.
The humans prepare
to fight back.
Both soldiers and adventurers
unite against the monsters.
The task of defeating the demon
Jaldabaoth is left to Momon,
Nabe, and Evileye. A symbol
of hope for mankind,
Momon turns his
blade to the demon.
Chapter Thirteen:
"The Ultimate Trump Card."
I have everything well in hand.