[AINS] First up, the
supplemental funds for Sebas.
Next, is the reconstruction
and equipment fund for
the Lizard Men villages.
That leaves...
[MOMONGA]
Freakin' chump change!
Dammit all.
Why is there never enough money?
Maybe I should find a merchant
with deep pockets to sponsor me.
No. Momon is highly respected.
I can't have people thinking
he's only in it for the money.
Still. I really need the cash.
[knocking]
[AINS]
Enter.
Do you have news?
Yes, Mr. Momon, sir.
[AINS]
She's still doing that.
It's become a verbal
tic at this point.
[AINS]
What is it?
Forgive my intrusion,
but I thought
you would like to know
the iron ore you requested
has arrived and the merchant
is waiting for payment.
[AINS]
Excellent.
Take this and thank him for me.
May I ask why you ordered it
from so many different sources?
[AINS]
It's an experiment.
I'm learning how
the Exchange Box
appraises things in this world.
Understood, sir.
Then I will retrieve
the ore and report back.
[AINS]
Good.
And if the situation
should turn ugly,
how will you handle it?
Safety takes priority.
I will withdraw immediately.
Once I'm clear.
I will relocate to
the dummy Nazarick,
that Lady Aura constructed,
with all due haste.
And, in doing so,
confuse our enemies.
[AINS] Good. Avoid routes
with large crowds
where you can
easily be attacked.
And should any bystanders
accost or cat-call you,
do not injure them severely.
Keep your bloodlust in check,
and refrain from calling
humans "worms" or "insects."
Remember, we are
high-ranking adventurers.
Both our reputations
hinge on your restraint.
Right.
[AINS]
That is all. Good luck.
Sir.
[AINS] Hm... Expenses piling
up when you're broke
happens in every world, huh?
[CLIMB grunting]
[yells]
[GAZEF]
Why don't you call it a day?
[CLIMB]
Lord Stronoff.
There's no point in
overdoing it. Rest up.
Yes, you're right, of course.
Am I now?
If you really took
stock in my advice,
I wouldn't have
to waste my breath
reminding you every day.
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
Since you won't rest,
how about a practice match?
With you, sir?
Just recently,
I was shown how
callow I truly am.
I'd like to train with someone
who has a little resilience.
Callow? You, Lord? No way.
Yup.
If not for the aid of a merciful
and awe-inspiring caster,
there's a good chance
I wouldn't be standing
here right now.
What sort of magic
caster could do that?
His name is Ains Ooal Gown.
He is incredible.
Even the Baharuth Empire's
freakish wizard
wouldn't stand a chance.
At least, that's what
I think of him.
I'll be sure to remember him.
You can count on that, my lord.
But are... you sure
you wanna train
with someone as
inexperienced as me?
It's not training.
Just practicing with swords.
Whether you learn something from
it or not is entirely up to you.
[GAZEF] Now, give it
everything you've got.
Any day now.
If you won't, that's fine.
I will!
[CLIMB grunts]
[CLIMB yelps]
Just because a sword
is all I'm carrying
doesn't mean you should
focus your attention on it.
Change that, or you'll
wind up on the floor again.
Right.
Oh.
Very good, Climb.
A normal soldier would've
been done after that.
Princess Renner relies
on me for safety.
I have to become
stronger than I am.
Fine. Then stop waiting for me!
[CLIMB yells]
[GAZEF grunts]
[yells]
[CLIMB grunting]
I told you, stop focusing on
what's in my damn hand!
Martial Art Fortress!
You baited me?
That's right!
Here we go! Martial Art, Slash!
[GAZEF grunts]
[CLIMB grunts]
[pants]
You surprised me.
Now I'm going to take this
a bit more seriously.
I hoped you would!
[CLIMB yells]
[CLIMB panting]
[GAZEF]
How about it?
I think I did a good job
of controlling myself,
considering your bones
are still intact.
I'm just bruised. That's all.
A little rest and I'm good.
[GAZEF] You'll be off to guard
the Princess soon, right?
Yes, sir.
Drink this. It'll fix
the worst of it.
Thank you very much, my lord.
You really are amazing,
you know? How did you...?
If you're asking how
I got this strong,
you're out of luck.
I don't have a good
answer for you.
I simply have a talent
for the art of combat.
But, Climb, you have
that same talent.
All you have to do is hone it.
[CLIMB]
You think so?
Yeah.
But that formal training
is holding you back.
You can't help but focus on
fighting with the sword alone.
That'll get you killed
in the heat of battle.
The sword is just one
means of attacking.
Try to incorporate your hands,
feet, knees, elbows--
your whole body
into your method.
If you don't mind fighting
like a muddy
adventurer, that is.
I learned a lot from you today.
Thank you very much.
That strike from above
is one of your best abilities.
However, you should think about
what you're going to do
next as a follow through.
Right! I will!
[VICE CHIEF]
Chief Warrior.
If you'll excuse me.
What is it, Vice-Chief?
This is bad, sir.
The boy is bodyguard
to the Princess.
If word got out that he fought
the chief royal warrior,
and either of you lost,
the Noble Faction
would have a field day.
I just wanted to
spar with someone
who could keep me
on my toes for a bit.
[VICE CHIEF] Well, I don't
think anyone saw you,
but you should be more
careful from now on.
His common heritage
is only compounded
by the fact that he's an
orphan from God knows where.
The Noble Faction's antipathy
toward him is pretty strong.
So, do you think you
can help him improve?
Sadly, he's as strong
as he's ever going to be.
He's what adventurers would
call "capped at gold."
But while he's limited
by his ability,
he's not limited by experience.
Only time will tell.
Hold on.
Gazef, is that Prince Zanac
with Marquis Raeven?
Why would someone
of the Noble Faction
be with the Prince?
Does he intend to switch
to the Royal Faction?
Very possible--
that Marquis is a
shameless opportunist.
Wouldn't shock me
to see him anywhere.
Who knows what he's
working behind the scenes.
[gasps]
Ah, the ever-dutiful Climb.
On your way to visit
that monster, I presume?
I am.
With all due respect, Highness,
Princess Renner is a kindhearted
and beautiful treasure
of the kingdom.
I'm not the one who
called her a monster,
and I will deny anyone
who says otherwise.
[gasps]
But a "beautiful
treasure," well,
considering the money
she's wasted on commoners
and the prohibition
of transit-tariffs.
I hardly think "treasure"
is appropriate.
Highness.
I believe Princess Renner
proposed the measure
that abolished the slave
trade within the kingdom.
Surely that has merit.
A rare exception, that.
But what about
the others, Marquis?
She knows her goal
is impossible,
so she throws darts in the dark
with no regard to who she hits.
I'm certain she wouldn't
do such a thing, Lord.
I'm sure you are.
Would you deliver a message
to that monster for me?
If given the chance,
our elder brother
will use her as a
political instrument,
but if she works with me,
he will graciously relieve her
of her title as Princess
and grant her a comfortable
plot of land out
in the frontier.
[gasps] Surely you jest, Lord.
I'll pretend I didn't
hear that, for your sake.
What a shame. I thought
it was quite good.
[ZANAC]
One more thing.
Marquis Raeven and I
are of the same mind
when it comes to that
girl and her "policies."
I dare say our joining
forces will prove to be
the last nail in Renner's
proverbial coffin.
Prince Zanac.
Don't worry about it, Marquis.
I'm fairly certain that
monster is quite aware
of our opinion of her.
[MAID 7A] Goodness, what's
a commoner doing in here?
[MAID 7B]
The princess has bizarre tastes.
[MAID 7A]
Definitely.
[sighs]
[CLIMB]
Pardon me.
I was wondering where you were.
Morning, Princess.
Sorry I'm late. Lady Aindra.
Uh.
Oh, her. She's a
member of my team.
[RENNER]
This is Tina.
My apologies. It's a
pleasure to meet you.
My name is Climb.
I'm well aware
of your exploits--
of all Blue Rose's
members, in fact.
You're practically
living legends.
[TINA]
Pleasure.
Thanks for looking after
my fiendish boss' friend.
We were just getting to
the meat of the discussion.
Why don't you join us?
I'm your bodyguard.
It would be inappropriate.
[LAKYUS]
It makes no difference to me.
My lady. I couldn't possibly.
Enough with formality.
Just call me Lakyus.
Special men get that privilege.
"Special"?
Please don't joke
like that, my lady.
Wait, she was joking?
'Course I was, sweetie.
I mean, Climb is special,
don't get me wrong,
but it's because he's your man.
I was just having fun.
You're incorrigible.
Now, sit down and drink
before your tea gets cold.
Don't worry, Tina's
the only one who bites.
[RENNER] Now, back to
what we were discussing.
About Eight Fingers, right?
Where'd we leave off?
I'm pretty sure I covered
how we burned the fields
they used for producing
Black Dust materials.
Yes.
On that note, I can't thank
you and Blue Rose enough.
My brother and the
nobles do nothing
but quarrel among themselves.
If they keep allowing
Eight Fingers to secretly
do business in the
kingdom's shadows,
it will fall into ruin.
Our nation will crumble
from the inside out.
However,
I don't have any
influential backing
or a military force
at my discretion.
I'm sorry.
It's just, since
Eight Fingers has ties
to the noble and royal factions,
I must put the burden on
adventurer's like Blue Rose.
No need for apologies.
We're friends, after all.
Tina, give her the parchment.
[LAKYUS] We found this in
the village where they were
producing Black Dust.
Know what it is?
It's a substitution cipher.
[BOTH gasp]
Interesting.
I wonder why they
left it behind?
A trap? Or for
some other reason?
And if it was a trap,
why use something so hard?
Be right back.
I have a hunch that
cracking this code
will prove fairly easy.
Unbelievable.
You got that right.
I don't understand
why she thinks
she's powerless to help anyone.
Of all the people I know,
she's the only one
I would call a genius
and mean it.
Well, it isn't orders from
their higher ups, sadly.
But it is a list of
villages and buildings.
Seven of which
are in the capital.
Do you think they're
Black Dust stockpiles
or other critical
production sites?
I doubt they'd leave
anything that important
at a production site or
written in such an easy code.
I think... it was bait.
[BOTH]
They tricked us?
[RENNER] Not exactly.
Eight Fingers is divided up
into eight different
organizations, right?
Yeah, that's the rumor, anyway.
There's smuggling,
slave trading, gambling,
illegal drugs and each
one has its own chief.
Then I believe these are bases
for the other organizations.
They need our
attention diverted
until they can get
things back on track.
And they're using their
own partners as bait?
That underground brothel's
not on the list.
[LAKYUS]
What is it?
I'm confused.
I thought that
such establishments
had been done away with
thanks to the princess.
Mostly.
Abolishing the slave trade
did a lot of good.
But, unfortunately,
one Eight Fingers brothel
is still active
here in the capital.
Tell me, Renner,
what would you say
to Blue Rose raiding the place
and putting an end to it
once and for all?
If it turned up some
evidence as a result,
it would strike a powerful
blow against the nobles
who are in bed
with Eight Fingers.
I appreciate your willingness,
but I would hate
to create trouble for
you and your family.
On the other hand,
it would be too much
for Climb to handle alone.
I'm terribly sorry for my
lack of strength, Princess.
Forgive me, Climb,
that was careless!
That isn't what I was
implying at all, okay?
I rely on you more
than anyone, Climb.
I can't begin to thank you
for how hard you work,
even when you don't
think I'm looking.
Just, please, don't do
anything too foolhardy.
In fact, I order you not to.
You see, if anything
happened to you, I'd...
I would...
[clears throat]
In any case, while we
can't ignore the brothel,
we should discuss the other
locations on this paper
and what to do about them
before they catch on.
You're right. We should take
advantage of the opportunity.
They still haven't
realized we're responsible
for the village attack.
However, they have got to
know that this information
has been leaked by now.
Is it okay if we borrow
Climb for a little while?
I'd like him to tell
Gagaran and the others
that we're making
our move right away.
Understood, Lady Aindra!
[LAKYUS muffled] Come to think
of it, Tina's investigation
turned up the names
of several nobles...
My, my.
Sounds like the Princess is
doing something reckless again.
Must be tough on those
Blue Rose ladies.
I'm afraid that one of
those nobleman's daughters
is currently serving
me as a maid.
Well, it doesn't
seem likely that
she was sent here just
to spy on you, but still.
Yes, I know.
I'll have to tell Climb to be
extra careful from now on.
Welcome back, my lord.
I've been waiting.
That's very thoughtful of you.
I trust there were no
problems with your work?
[TUARE]
No, none.
Well done, Tuare.
I'm glad to hear it.
Have you decided what we're
having for dinner tonight?
A stew, Lord.
Made with chopped potatoes.
If it proves to be as tasty
as your previous dishes,
I'm looking forward to it.
You don't mean that.
I wouldn't lie to you, Tuare.
Are you sure you have all
the ingredients for the dish?
No. Sorry, I'll
check on it later.
We can go shopping
together if you like.
[TUARE]
No, that's all right.
Do not worry.
I understand your fear.
I'm not angry.
You must be terrified
of going outside.
But, please, rest assured.
I made a promise to
protect you, Tuare.
No matter what perils
may come your way.
I will dash them to pieces.
You have my word.
Tuare, keep moving forward.
If you're scared, I don't mind
if you close your eyes to do it.
All I ask is you trust
me to lead the way.
Lord Sebas, you
aren't being fair.
You aren't.
There is no way I could possibly
say no to you after that.
And don't worry about me.
I may not look it but
I'm strong, I assure you.
As a matter of fact,
there are only 41 others
who are stronger than me.
At least, they're the
only ones I'm aware of.
Is that a lot? Forty-one?
[chuckles]
[knocking]
I've returned and am at
your service, my lady.
Very good. Thank you, Sebas.
Are you certain we should not
inform Lord Ains about her?
I imagine he requires you
to be in daily contact with him.
Could you not simply make
mention of that woman
the next time you report in?
First off, I have an
extremely high regard
for her culinary abilities,
Solution. Secondly,
if any humans were
to see us living alone
in this mansion,
it might raise suspicion
and spur them to
scrutinize our presence.
So, she's part of
a diversionary tactic?
[SEBAS] Yes and if I
were to seek permission
from Lord Ains over
a matter as simple
as maintaining our cover,
he's likely to snap
and tell me to think for myself.
[STAFFAN] I am Staffan Havish,
a constable charged
with keeping the peace here
in our glorious capital.
What can I do
for you, Constable?
[STAFFAN]
There's an establishment, well,
his establishment, actually.
Call me Succulent.
A pleasure to meet you, my lady.
I received a disturbing report
from an eyewitness recently.
Apparently, someone with
a scroll bearing the seal
of the magicians' guild,
gave him an exorbitant
amount of money and made off
with one of his employees.
Sounds like a clear violation
of our slave trade
prohibition. So, my lady.
Has someone in your house
been especially naughty?
This is boring.
[STAFFAN]
Huh?
[SOLUTION]
I will let my butler, Sebas,
deal with this touchy matter.
I'm sure he can handle
things from here.
Good day, gentlemen.
Now then, as my
lady has ordered.
I will listen to
what you have to say
and take whatever
action is necessary.
[STAFFAN] Well, from the
circumstantial evidence alone,
it is beyond a doubt that
you have committed a crime.
Fortunately for you
and your mistress,
he's a benevolent man and is
willing to offer you clemency
which will, naturally,
take the form of consolation
payments and commissions.
[SEBAS] I see. And how
much will that cost?
Five hundred gold.
Not a copper less.
That is beyond extortionate.
The girl was in a terrible
state when I found her.
If you were to
take her away now,
she might very well die from it.
You don't say. How tragic.
In the interest of my
dear employee's welfare,
what would you say to loaning us
the lady of your house, instead?
While the girl recovers.
Oh, indeed!
Your lost income
must be compensated!
Your excessive lust must
be a problem for you.
Ah! How dare you! Lust has
nothing to do with it!
I am merely upholding the law
that came at the noble
behest of the eminent
Golden Princess Renner!
I will not stand here
and suffer your insults!
Now, now, there's no reason
to let your blood
boil, Lord Havish.
We'll return the day after
tomorrow for your decision.
I hope, for your sake,
it's the right one, Sebas.
We'll see, won't we?
May I ask what you plan to do?
[SEBAS] I think I'll go for a
short stroll and think it over.
[SOLUTION]
Message.
Hello? Lord Ains?
Can you hear me?
[AINS]
Solution?
I'm surprised to
have you contact me.
Is something wrong?
I think...
...there's a chance that
Lord Sebas has turned on us.
[AINS]
Mm... U-Uh, really?
[AINS clears throat]
No kidding around.
If you don't have proof
of this accusation,
punishment will be swift.
Is there any?
Yes, Lord.
[AINS] In search of the
strength to protect his master,
Climb puts forth
relentless effort.
In the eyes of those
stronger than he,
Climb has no potential
physically or with magic.
Knowing this, Climb presses on,
until eventually,
his search for strength brings
him to meet a powerful old man.
Chapter 8: "A boy's feeling".
If you wish for strength,
show your resolve.