[SEBAS] This leads into
the heart of the brothel.
It extends underground.
And, according to the assassin,
there's a secondary entrance
somewhere in that building.
All right then.
If you're planning
to launch your attack
from the front,
why don't Climb and I
find the backdoor?
He can keep watch
once we do that.
Meanwhile, I'll work
my way to you.
[SEBAS]
Very well.
Good plan, Lord Unglaus.
I'm all for it.
[BRAIN] Can we drop the
formal talk, please?
You can just call me Brain.
In fact, I'd strongly
prefer if you did.
[SEBAS]
All right. Let's move in.
[BRAIN, CLIMB]
Right.
One more thing.
I'll take as many prisoners as
I can, but if anyone resists,
I will kill them
without remorse.
Do you have a problem with that?
Killing's unavoidable
at this point.
The three of us can't
arrest everyone in there.
That said, if one of them
happens to be a captain
of Eight Fingers, may I ask
that you please take
them alive instead?
Of course, young Climb.
I'm not a hardened killer.
It's not as if I'm here simply
to butcher the lot of them.
Rest easy.
Picking locks is not
one of my specialties.
[yawns]
[bang]
What the hell?
Hey, what's that racket?
[MEN gasp]
Could you fetch your manager?
I have a few complaints
that need to be
addressed personally.
[MAN 9C grunts]
[bell rings]
[CLIMB] There's a
secret door, all right.
Ah. That's a pretty
handy item you've got.
[CLIMB]
Yes.
A certain Lady gave me these
for just such an occasion.
They should make up for
our lack of a Thief.
[bell rings]
[CLIMB] Sure enough.
It was booby-trapped.
[BRAIN]
A poison arrow. So, what now?
It'd be best if you could
cover this door for me.
Mind waiting here?
I'm not very good
at indoor combat.
If there are more
open areas downstairs
I'd rather fight there.
'Kay. Shall we go then?
Yes.
[STAFFAN grunting]
Hey, what's wrong?
Are you through already? Huh?
[WOMAN 9A sputters]
You're not bad,
but the girl who ran away
had a scream that
really drove me wild.
[STAFFAN laughs]
[door opens]
So, hitting brings you
pleasure, is that it?
Why are you here?
[yelps]
[STAFFAN whimpers]
You bastard!
You won't get away--
Mercy, please!
What, don't you like it?
Of course not!
Now stop it--don't you
know who I am?
A mere fool. Nothing more.
For Heaven's sake.
What an awful sight.
Idiot--
[STAFFAN]
Intruder! Come quick!
Why isn't anyone
coming out to help me?
[SEBAS]
Simple.
They are either unconscious
or dead and rotting.
Huh? That's impossible,
you're lying!
Now then.
I feel no need to spare your
life, after what I've seen.
Seems fitting you
should die here.
No, no, wait! Please!
Why are you doing this?
In light of everything
you've done,
you still don't
realize you deserve
to be brought to justice?
Despicable.
I could make you
a very rich man.
Just name your price!
This is what it means to be
truly unworthy of life.
[STAFFAN grunts]
[SEBAS]
Stay there and rot.
[bell rings]
[door opens]
[tapping]
[MEN chattering]
Sounds like a real
party in there.
Be on guard.
You wanna wait for me here?
Yes.
I'm going to pop in for a bit
and see if Sebas needs help.
Don't get yourself killed.
[CLIMB]
Wasn't planning on it, Lord--
Huh?
Just come back
in one piece, Brain.
Empty? Weird.
Yeah, that's not happening.
How about this one?
[CLIMB]
What are these? Spare uniforms?
[crash]
The alarm indicated
the intruders
were already past here.
That was the point of using the
secret passage to sneak out.
Calm yourself.
Whining about it won't
do us any good, will it?
You're from Eight Fingers.
[COCCO DOLL] Ah! I know
this boy! He's the underling
of that wretched harpy,
Princess Renner!
[SUCCULENT]
That he is, Cocco Doll.
I wouldn't mind having
him for my collection.
Catch him for me?
I'll have to charge a
separate fee, but sure.
[COCCO DOLL]
Okay.
[inhales]
I need some help down here!
Sorry, Coco, but we can't risk
taking him back if he
has allies nearby.
What do you mean?
You're the famous
Illusion Demon, right?
Or is the name just for show?
Illusions?
I'll have to deal
with him before
any reinforcements
come barging in.
But, I doubt it will
be too problematic.
Just remember that we can't
prevail until you escape.
We can't afford anymore
distractions after--
I'm gonna guard this door
no matter what it takes.
As long as nothing
happens to me.
I swear neither of you
will leave this room!
Those are some ballsy
claims, little man.
Let's see if you
can back 'em up.
[cackles]
[gasps]
[SUCCULENT growls]
[yelps]
[groans]
Oh.
Thank you!
Sorry, got distracted.
S'no good. I've gotta
kill this kid.
No! He will make a
perfect card to play
against the sniffling
Princess. I won't lose him!
He was trying to feed
us false information.
He may have friends
inside the brothel,
but the upstairs
is probably clear.
Meaning?
He's the only one blocking
our path to safety.
If you wanna get out before
his friends come back,
then I have to cut him
down, here and now.
[CLIMB]
Is that a Martial Art skill?
Fighting defensively won't work.
Which means...
[CLIMB yells]
[yells]
So that's your trick!
[SUCCULENT]
Hm?
[CLIMB] Your right arm
itself is the illusion!
Your actual arm and sword
have turned invisible!
Not bad. I'm impressed, kid.
Yes, I've trained in
both the Illusionist
and Fencer character classes.
My "trick" is nothing more
than an invisibility spell
combined with illusion magic.
Simple, yes, but really
quite effective.
Most don't catch on so quickly.
Seeing as how I've
divided my abilities.
I may be considered your lesser,
at least when it comes
to prowess in combat.
That said, are you
able to discriminate
between reality and
utter fiction?
Multiple Vision.
Martial Art! Ability Boost!
Mental Enhancement!
[CLIMB grunts]
[yells]
[SUCCULENTS]
Scintillating Scotoma.
[CLIMB grunts]
[SUCCULENTS]
Wrong one!
Quick Evasion!
[CLIMB]
This one!
Fifty-fifty shot!
[SUCCULENT grunts]
[gasps]
I guess... I can't
say I've won yet.
But I can apprehend
Succulent, at least.
[grunts]
[SUCCULENT]
Unfortunately for you,
that's not going to happen.
Fox Sleep.
An illusion spell that
kicks in after an injury.
Nice swipe, by the way.
But, I'm afraid you
missed the mark.
And we're out of
time so, say goodbye.
[COCCO DOLL] Are you sure we
can't take him back with us?
[SUCCULENT]
Give me a break.
The kid's pals could come
rushing through the door
any second, and I don't
plan to be here.
You need to let it go--
[gasps]
[panting]
[CLIMB]
I can't quit yet.
Not until I've repaid
Princess Renner.
I owe her too much to die!
How? How'd you...?
That should have been
a mortal wound!
You shouldn't be standing!
Why don't you just die!
What?
Your strength should
be drained by now!
[CLIMB grunts]
[yelps]
[SUCCULENT] Damn it.
I wasn't watching your feet.
[CLIMB panting]
So, you were running
on adrenaline, huh?
Figures. You're not
much of a fighter.
[BRAIN]
Not another step.
Huh?
Just in time I see.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and kill them both!
If I try, he'll rush me,
and cut me down with
a single strike.
Ah-- Oh.
Easy now. You're badly hurt.
Do you have any magic items
that can heal the wound?
Uh-huh. In... bag.
Good man.
From here on out,
you'll face me.
And I'll make you pay for
what you did to him.
What should they put
on your tombstone?
I'm Lord Brain Unglaus
Unglaus? You gotta
be kidding me!
No way! It's really him?
[BRAIN] You know, the
old me might have been
swelling with pride about now.
Most of the people I've
met today already knew me.
But, things are a lot
more complicated
than they used to be.
Hey. We don't have to fight.
Why not call this
whole thing off, huh?
After all, we're two of a kind.
What we want--what we
need is power! Right?
There's a place for you
in Eight Fingers, Brain.
It's the perfect
organization for men
with our kind of
insatiable appetites.
You want magical items?
We've got plenty!
High-value weapons and
protective gear, too--
Enough with the sales pitch.
[gasps]
[BRAIN]
Is that all you people are?
What?
[BRAIN]
Hate to break it to you,
but, our power means nothing.
Not in this world.
Also, there's one
thing I've learned.
Strength on behalf of others
surpasses any one
person's might.
Maybe that lesson's sounds like
nothing special, but still.
I've learned it. Thankfully.
That's a shame, Unglaus, really.
I was hoping I wouldn't
have to kill a warrior
as gifted as you today,
but hey, life just
ain't fair sometimes.
Think that you can?
Then, please, go on and show
me what a sell sword can do.
You've got me curious.
Are you mocking me?
That'll cost you dearly!
I'll kill you, then I'll slice
your little friend bit by bit!
Be extra careful.
Succulent uses
illusion techniques.
What you see isn't
necessarily reality!
Interesting.
I guess that does make
him a tricky opponent.
I'll finish this...
in one strike.
[SUCCULENTS]
What?
Don't pretend like you
didn't hear me, Succulent.
Bring it.
[SUCCULENTS]
All right. It's your funeral!
[gasps]
[SUCCULENT groans]
[BRAIN]
My Field can detect anything,
even if it's been
turned invisible.
I saw you were going for Climb
while I was distracted
by your duplicates,
but you tried it with
the wrong opponent.
Life ain't fair sometimes.
One strike, just
like I promised.
[CLIMB]
Nicely done!
[SEBAS]
Indeed.
[groans]
[BRAIN]
When did you get here?
Why, just now, Lord Brain.
[CLIMB]
You did? Crazy.
I couldn't detect any
of his movements,
even with my Field up.
Lord Sebas...
who the hell are you?
[CLIMB]
All of the women have been
put in protective custody.
Thank you for all your help.
I have to stay here and deliver
the after-incident report.
I assume you're leaving?
Yeah.
I worked up a hell of
an appetite in there.
Farewell. Until we meet again.
[SOLUTION]
Welcome back, Lord Sebas.
We've been waiting for you.
Do not dawdle.
Lord Ains is here and does
not wish to be kept waiting.
[RENNER] Is that you,
Climb? Please, come in.
I'm sorry for being
gone so long, Princess.
I was terribly worried.
I couldn't help but
fear the worst for you.
Let's talk.
I want to know everything
that happened today.
[RENNER]
I see.
Tomorrow, or, at least
the day after that,
we'll be staging attacks on
seven of their facilities.
After your raid on the brothel,
we can assume that
Eight Fingers' security
will grow tighter
as more time passes.
I'm so sorry.
I've jeopardized
your operations.
Please, don't let it bother you.
We've made our
intentions clear now.
In just one day,
they've lost Succulent,
as well as Coco Doll, the head
of their slave trade division.
This will be enough to
shake the very pillars
of their organization.
That is why
I plan to strike them again,
as soon as possible.
They'll have more
than a bloody nose
before they leave the city.
So how about it? You in?
Always, Princess.
It sounds like tomorrow
will be a rather hectic day.
Please watch yourself.
Right!
[GAZEF]
Wait.
Climb took on a
member of Six Arms?
Yeah!
He was in a bad way
when I got there,
but it looked like he had
Succulent cornered pretty good.
I'll be...
That said, he has no real
talent with the sword.
So much so, that when
I first saw him,
I pegged him as a poor
little kid playing knight
and vainly struggling for power.
But then, he faced
absolute terror.
The kind that rivaled the
monster I ran away from,
and he came out on top.
In that regard,
the boy's better than me.
It's hard to believe, ain't it?
Uh-huh. This world's
full of surprises.
The person who gave Climb
this "special" training
you mentioned is one thing,
but this monster you ran into
really piqued my interest.
Her name is
Shalltear Bloodfallen.
A vampire, most likely.
She stopped the technique
I made to beat you
with just one hand. Even yawned.
You don't say.
Do me a favor.
If you see her, don't try
to fight her. Just run.
Well, I appreciate the concern.
But, if anything threatens
my King or country,
I'll happily die to defend them.
Even if it's against this
"Shallty" monster of yours.
That's "Shalltear," got it?
Shalltear Bloodfallen!
Hey, careful. You'll get
some on the bread!
That's fine by me.
Anything to make these
moldy bricks taste better.
My sense of taste
is shot. I don't care.
Don't tell me yours
is, too, Unglaus.
No formalities. Call me
Brain from now on.
Okay. Only if you'll
call me Gazef.
[BRAIN]
Now that's more like it.
[CLIMB]
I'm off. Good night, Princess.
[RENNER]
Good night.
[RENNER] Now then,
who's the maid on duty?
Ah yes, the insolent wench.
[RENNER] The one I've
overheard making fun
of my precious Climb.
Let's see.
Which face am I
supposed to wear, again?
This is the smile
I use when receiving
others as a princess.
I think this one will do nicely.
[bell rings]
[knocking]
You rang, my princess?
I would like to take a bath.
Would you kindly draw
one for me, please?
Yes, right away, my princess.
[giggles]
You seem quite cheerful.
For good reason!
My Climb performed
an incredible feat today.
[MAID 7B] I'd say
congratulations are in order.
Agreed!
He put down a group
of terribly evil men.
Then, he freed some
unfortunate souls
who had been held captive...
[RENNER] I'll kill her.
Just like the rest.
[MAID 7B]
That's incredible!
[RENNER] And if anyone
else dares to make fun
of my precious Climb...
[RENNER]
...I'll kill them, too.
I'll have to apologize
to Coco Doll
next time I see him.
I thought Succulent would
be able to handle things,
but I guess I was wrong.
This place still fell
like a fort of straw.
[EDSTROM chuckles]
Succulent's a fool.
Just say the word,
and he'll breathe his last.
A fool he may be,
but he has his uses.
Reach out to the count.
I want him back on the
streets within the day.
[MALMVIST]
So, what do we do? Step back?
I see no benefit in retaliating.
The losses we'd take
are too great.
Don't be ridiculous.
We have to make an example out
of those that hit the brothel.
Six Arms has a
reputation, after all.
Don't even consider
losses at this point.
Undead King, Davernoch.
Spatial Slash, Peshurian.
Edstrom, the Dancing Scimitar.
And Malmvist,
of the Thousand Kills.
We'll handle this ourselves,
and we'll do it our way.
Whoever attacked us
will soon know
the true meaning of suffering.
By the time we're
through with them,
they'll be begging for
death and hellfire.
[AINS] A report of Sebas's
possible betrayal reaches Ains.
[AINS] It is hard to believe
that the fiercely loyal Sebas
would ever betray Nazarick,
but the truth must be confirmed.
Sebas responds to the summons.
Meanwhile, Renner has an
interesting conversation
over tea at the castle.
Chapter Ten: "Disturbance begins
in the royal capital."
Tell me what you treasure most.