[AINS]
Good.
We can finally get
down to business.
I'm sure I don't need to explain
my presence to you, Sebas.
Correct?
No, there is no need, my lord.
[AINS]
Where's your handkerchief?
You're sweating something awful.
Here. I'll lend you mine.
[knocking]
I have brought her, my lord.
[AINS]
Come in, Tuare.
I wish to see Sebas' human
pet with my own eyes.
[AINS]
Good. You didn't run.
On your kn--
[AINS]
No!
Control spells are unnecessary.
I will permit her indecorum
as a sign of respect
for her bravery.
I am Ains Ooal Gown.
You would do well
to remember it,
for I am the master of
everyone here, including Sebas.
Uh! Right.
[AINS]
Now then. Sebas.
I thought I instructed you
to avoid drawing attention.
Yes.
[AINS]
Nonetheless, you have courted
calamity for the sake
of this no-account woman.
Am I wrong?
Forgive me, Lord Ains.
I am deeply sorry
that my indiscretion
has caused you trouble.
Nothing like this will
happen again on my watch,
you have my word.
[AINS]
Enough.
Everyone makes mistakes,
including me.
Be at ease. This blunder is
trivial, so I will forgive it.
Thank you, Lord.
I am most grateful.
[AINS] However, you must still
make amends for your error.
Kill her.
My lord. Is that necessary?
[AINS] Are you a loyal
dog that serves me,
the 41, or a stray that
follows its own will?
Think hard before you answer.
Well, I--
[AINS]
Not with words, fool!
Show me through your actions.
[SEBAS grunts]
What is this?
[AINS]
Step away, Sebas!
Right, Lord.
[AINS]
Cocytus, would you say
he deliberately put enough
force into that attack
to kill this girl?
[COCYTUS]
Without a doubt, Lord.
[AINS]
In that case,
I take it as undeniable proof
that Sebas' loyalty is genuine.
This pleases me to no end.
Lord.
[AINS] Now, let's move on
to the next topic.
After an in-depth assessment,
I believe you've gathered
sufficient information.
I've decided to
vacate this mansion
and return to Nazarick.
As for the fate of the
woman, give me some time.
I do not think death
will be necessary,
but I'm not yet certain of it.
Demiurge, I will be taking
Victim back with me.
Right.
[AINS]
Greater Teleportation!
All of this has
taken a toll on her.
I think it would be best
if she returned to her room.
Since there's no
longer an issue,
I will escort her there myself.
With your permission,
of course, Lord Demiurge.
I suppose.
Do what you must, Sebas.
[SEBAS]
I do not intend to apologize.
But, I am certain that if I had
gone about this a different way,
I would not have to break
my promise to you now.
What are you telling me?
[SEBAS] To go and live a happy
life in the world of humans.
Lord Ains should be able to
erase all your bad memories.
You can start over.
Live free and happy.
But, what about you?
I think it best if you
forget me as well.
After all, there's nothing
good about me to remember.
[TUARE]
What do mean, "nothing good"?
The only reason I'm happy
is because I'm with you,
don't you see that?
This is the first home
I haven't thought of as hell.
You gave me meals, a warm bed,
and a decent, rewarding job.
I was born and raised in a small
farming village, you see.
My life was as difficult
there as in the brothel.
We would tend to the fields
with empty stomachs
and dry throats.
Only to have the
feudal lord take away
most of our crop yield.
Those of us that didn't
starve went mad with hunger.
Not to mention, the way
our lord treated us
as his personal playthings.
Even when I screamed,
he would keep laughing as
he violated me. He laughed!
[SEBAS]
All right.
It may mean your death.
[TUARE] I would rather remember
and be killed at your hand.
At least I would die
having felt warmth
and happiness for a time.
Tuare.
I will ask permission
to take you back with me,
if that's truly what you wish.
[TUARE]
Thank you, Lord Sebas.
[SEBAS]
But first, I must ask.
Do you have any attachment
to the world of humans?
I would kind of like to see
my younger sister again one day.
But my desire to not
remember my painful past
far outweighs any other
desires I may have.
Very well then.
Go. Rest in your room for now.
I will go to Lord Ains again
and make the request.
'Kay.
[SEBAS grunts]
That tickled my chin.
I've never had a happy kiss.
Thanks for that.
Thank you for
indulging me, Lord.
Is something wrong?
Your face is flushed red.
You need not worry.
I am fine, my lord.
There's no need
for titles with me.
[COCYTUS]
I don't need it, either.
[SEBAS]
All right.
[AINS]
Good, you're all here. Rise.
I believe that went well.
How about you, Demiurge?
Have your anxious
thoughts been abated?
I, for one, never questioned
Sebas' loyalty
to me or Nazarick.
[DEMIURGE]
Yes, Lord, I am satisfied.
And I am deeply sorry
for my lack of faith.
Despite your trust in him,
you granted my request
to test his loyalty and
it's greatly appreciated.
[AINS] It's no matter.
I have oversights, as well.
Now, you wished to
discuss how to deal
with that human woman, Sebas?
I do.
[AINS] I assume you're
worried that she could
leak information about Nazarick
once she's been released?
Then, after her
memories are re-arranged,
you may provide her with
coin and relocate her.
If I may, killing her would
guarantee our safety, my lord.
[AINS]
No.
I am not one who resorts
to homicidal acts
when it gains me nothing.
[DEMIURGE]
Understood, Lord.
In that case, what if I put
her to work in my stockyards?
[AINS]
Hm. Yes, that could work nicely.
If I may, Lord.
[AINS]
Mm. What is it, Sebas?
There is another solution.
I would like to put
the girl to work
in the Great Tomb of Nazarick,
if you're willing.
[gasps]
[COCYTUS]
Hm?
[AINS]
I'll ask you the same thing
I asked Cocytus recently.
Will taking her in
benefit me in any way?
Yes. Tuare's an
exceptional cook.
Since only a few in Nazarick
possess that skill,
adding her to our
number will help
lighten the load,
if only a little.
[AINS]
Indeed.
I, too, have been
considering that very point.
[DEMIURGE] But, Lord, are we
certain this stray human
can prepare food
worthy of Nazarick?
[SEBAS] Tuare seems well versed
in cooking household fare.
Whether or not it's
"worthy," I couldn't say.
I, for one, believe
something as common
as steamed potatoes has
no place in the Tomb.
[SEBAS] I cannot help but
think you are being too haste
in your judgement.
If she is skilled
with homely meals,
then she is capable of mastering
other forms of cooking.
We should look to the future.
[DEMIURGE] In that case,
I would like her to help
with the cooking at
my stockyard, first.
Making mincemeat for Abelion
sheep is no easy chore.
[SEBAS]
I would be against that.
--Her talents would go to waste.
--[TOUCH ME] Come on, Ulbert.
[TOUCH ME] We put farming
the rare drop from Surt,
the Fire Giant on the guild
calendar a few days ago.
How could you forget?
[ULBERT] You're the one
whose forgotten, Touch.
We still have several members
who need to complete
the Ice Dragon Hunt event,
so that they can unlock the
ability to change classes.
[TOUCH ME] Yes, but Surt's
drop rate is much lower
than the Ice Dragon's.
It'd be far more efficient
to take care of it first.
[ULBERT]
Unbelievable.
You can be such a spoiled
freakin' brat sometimes.
[TOUCH ME] Look who's talking,
Mr. Pouty-Mc-Goat Face!
The Ice Dragon is much more...
[DEMIURGE] I'm not trying
to assign blame, I simply--
[COCYTUS]
Shut up already!
We are in the presence
of Lord Ains!
Pardon us, Lord!
We were careless.
[SEBAS] Our foolish
behavior was inexcusable.
[AINS laughs] I do not mind.
Please, be at ease.
I miss bickering like this!
[AINS laughs]
[AINS]
Inhibited again.
I'd like to speak
to Tuare once more.
Bring her here.
Right away.
I'll just be a moment.
[AINS]
She looks familiar.
Thanks for coming.
I have some questions.
But know that if your
answers are untruthful
or unsatisfactory, we are done.
You will lose your memories.
First, tell me your full name.
Okay. It's Tuareninya
Veyron, Lord.
[AINS]
You don't say.
All right then, Tuareninya.
Is your desire to go to
the Great Tomb of Nazarick?
To live among the inhuman there?
I am willing to give
you great wealth
and send you to a land
far away from here,
should you prefer it.
I wish to stay with Lord Sebas.
[AINS]
Very well.
My servants. I have decided.
[SERVANTS]
Lord!
[AINS]
In the name of Ains Ooal Gown,
Tuareninya is now
under my protection.
You will be
welcomed as my guest,
and want for nothing.
Thank you very much, my lord,
but if you'll allow it,
I would like to be put to
work alongside Lord Sebas.
[AINS]
If that is your wish, so be it.
Henceforth, you shall
work directly under Sebas
as a provisional maid.
At the same time,
Sebas will step down
from his role as leader
of the Pleiades.
The youngest of
the Seven Sisters,
Aureole Omega will
take his place.
Yuri Alpha will
be deputy leader.
Also, please inform
everyone in the Tomb
that I have personally
staked the great name
of Ains Ooal Gown on
Tuareninya's safety,
and that she will
work alongside them
from this day forward.
Demiurge, do you
have any objections
to my decision?
[DEMIURGE]
Not in the least, Supreme One.
[AINS] Then to confirm,
all the sentries posted
in this mansion will return
to Nazarick at once.
Sebas, Solution,
prepare to withdraw.
[DEMIURGE]
Lord Ains.
[AINS]
What is it, Demiurge?
[DEMIURGE]
The Abelion Sheep are omnivores,
so I would like to take
this opportunity to procure
a small amount of grain.
[AINS] I see. Sebas,
before you withdraw,
purchase a large amount of grain
and deliver it to
Demiurge for me.
As you wish, Lord Ains.
[DEMIURGE]
Forgive my curiosity,
but did you spare the girl
because you know her?
[AINS] I believe,
perhaps more than anything,
in returning kindness with
kindness, and evil with evil.
We should endeavor to
pay our debts back in full.
[AINS] This diary
belonged to a young girl,
broken hearted and
furious at the kidnapping
of her older sister.
To a certain degree,
it provided me
with a general knowledge
of this world.
I'm indebted to you, Ninya.
I can't repay you directly,
but I will do so
through your sister.
[DEMIURGE]
Lord Ains.
I'd like to make a request,
if you'll indulge me.
[AINS]
Mm.
After reading over
Sebas' findings,
there is one place
I would like to see.
Could I impose on you, Lord?
[AINS]
I don't mind.
You are acting for the benefit
of Nazarick, aren't you?
Go ahead. Enjoy.
I plan to, Lord.
[SEBAS]
We're going out for grain
and to pay respects
to some acquaintances.
We could be gone for some time.
[TUARE]
All right.
[SEBAS] Keep an eye on things
while we're gone, Tuare.
I will.
Don't worry, Lord Sebas.
[RENNER] Last night,
Climb captured the head
of Eight Fingers'
slave trade division.
[GAGARAN]
Not too shabby.
I think we should
alter our plan.
We'll launch simultaneous raids,
and take down all of
their strongholds at once.
If we wait too long,
we'll be at a disadvantage.
[GAGARAN] Well, yeah, but I
thought we were short-handed.
Can we pull it off?
I'm fairly certain
the nobleman I'm meeting
will be eager to lend a hand.
They're here, Princess.
Oh, whoa.
I was surprised to receive
a summons from you,
and intrigued.
It certainly piqued
my interest as well,
so I decided to tag along.
I trust you mind.
Oh, brother.
[RENNER] Thank you
for coming, so quickly.
I would like to ask for advice.
My advice? Really.
I believe that no one
in all the court
is better versed
in these matters
than you are, Marquis Raeven.
Bitter.
[RENNER] I can have
something sweeter made.
There's no need.
I'm sure we'd all like
to avoid any of these
chatty palace maids
seeing us together
and reporting it back
to their families.
Shall we dispense
with the pleasantries
and talk about what
you really want?
[ZANAC]
Don't ask for too much.
The Marquis may be one
of the Six Great Nobles
and a member of
the Noble Faction,
but he has his own
position to consider.
[RENNER]
Straight to the point, then.
Since you've been working with
the Royal Faction in secret,
I'd like you to
mobilize the military
[BOTH gasp]
[RENNER] True, it might
have been better to bring
this request to the three
Great Nobles who are publicly
aligned with the Royal Faction.
Sadly, one of them,
Marquis Bloomrush,
is a traitor, and has
been feeding information
to the Empire.
Just a moment, Princess Renner.
You knew, right?
Of course, the "shameless
opportunist" would never
be caught uninformed
in these dire times.
How else would you
manipulate the factions
to keep the kingdom intact?
That is why you
restrict the information
that flows his way, so he never
learns anything important.
Masterfully done, by the way.
You live like a bird
in a gilded cage up here.
How do you know this?
I get bits of information
and fill in the blanks.
The maids do love their gossip.
You truly are a monster.
[RENNER giggles]
Very well then.
I suppose we can
drop all pretense.
If that's okay with you, Prince.
But, before we do,
I would like to speak with the
real Princess Renner, please.
Magnificent!
It's better than I thought.
I remember seeing those eyes
when you were still a child!
You've just been
putting on an act?
I was, until I had
been fulfilled.
You mean that boy, Climb?
Yes indeed.
I'd marry him if I could.
Though, while I was at it,
I'd love chaining him up
and keeping him all to myself.
What joy I would feel!
"Keep"? I see.
It's an obsession, not love.
I am in love with him!
I adore his eyes, and the
way they look at me.
Not to mention the way
he follows me around
like a loyal dog on a leash.
So sorry. I'm quite confused.
I don't need you to
understand, dear brother.
As long as you know
that I am fond of Climb
and love him more than anything,
that is enough for me.
But Climb is just a commoner.
Marriage is impossible.
I'll make a deal with you.
Support my ascension, and I'll
make sure you get hitched.
I'm in!
That was quick.
The moment I saw you, brother.
I wanted nothing more than
to bring up that subject.
On that note.
I have another request
for you, Marquis Raeven.
I'm listening.
[RENNER]
Unless I'm mistaken,
you are father to a young boy?
Yes, he just turned five.
I would like for him
to be my betrothed.
No!
I will die before I give
my boy to a woman like you!
Please, excuse my
outburst, Highness.
Would you mind telling me
your reasons, Princess?
I'm sure you've figured it out.
You plan to marry my son,
but actually have your
children with Climb.
Then, my son could have children
with whichever woman he loved,
and they'd be successors.
Does that sum it up?
You're really proposing
this right in front of me?
Sure!
Better now than later,
don't you think?
--I hear...
--[RENNER] Yes?
...you plan to go up
against Eight Fingers.
I would like to strike at them
before they burrow too deeply,
but I need soldiers.
Where will you be attacking?
[RENNER]
Seven locations.
The problem is that each
of them are in territories
owned by different noblemen.
If we could uncover evidence
that ties them to Eight Fingers,
I could use it to exert pressure
and make the nobles compliant.
Or we could find something
during the attack.
Surely one of these
locations hides a secret.
Also, sister.
I have an important
question to ask you.
You're aware that our
beloved older brother
is also taking money
from Eight Fingers, right?
[gasps] Not Brother Barbro.
This could be our
opportunity to depose him!
We should definitely consider
including his drug division
stronghold in your
plan of attack.
Taking out eight
targets is obviously
better than seven.
As for soldiers.
I will send my own
guardsmen and faction military.
Though, even with
adequate numbers,
the real question is whether
we can hold our own
against the adamantite
members of Six Arms.
If needed, I can
call in a few favors
from the adventurer's guild.
[knocking]
He's here.
[RENNER] I think this
gentleman can handle Six Arms.
[SOLUTION] That took
longer than I expected.
But at least we know
the grain is secure.
We can return to
Nazarick without issue.
[SEBAS]
Tuare!
Tuare, are you here?
There are a number
of scratch markings
around the front door's keyhole.
Unless we have
three-foot-tall rodents,
someone must have
picked the lock.
Tuare's been kidnapped,
and I'm going to get her back.
They have left
instructions to meet them
at a particular time and place.
[SOLUTION] I wonder if
that's the best course.
Look.
I just mean you should inform
Lord Ains before you go,
or have you already
forgotten that he swore
to protect that
human girl of yours?
[gasps]
Report this to Lord Ains for me.
Tell him the situation and ask
what we should do about it.
[ALBEDO giggling]
--[beeping]
--[AINS] Albedo.
Yes, I hear you, Lord Ains.
Is there some way that
I might serve you?
[AINS] I just got a message
from Solution, or rather,
from Sebas through her.
Apparently the woman
he took in, Tuare,
has been abducted.
I am occupied at the moment.
Put together some
forces to back Sebas up.
Forgive my insolence, Lord.
You know I wouldn't
object without good cause.
But, I fail to see the value
in devoting our resources
to save an inferior creature.
[AINS]
No value?
I swore her safety on the
great name of Ains Ooal Gown.
My word is the most
valuable thing I can offer!
Is that clear?
If not, I'll spell
it out for you!
This affront cannot
be allowed to stand!
Even if they were
unaware of my word,
they will atone for it!
Sorry.
I have received your orders.
There is nothing you need
to apologize for, my lord.
The fault was mine entirely.
The girl will be rescued,
and I will personally make sure
these fools regret their folly.
[AINS] No need for that.
You organize them,
and Demiurge will
command them onsite.
[sighs] Still, I don't
understand. Ains Ooal Gown.
Ridiculous.
[AINS] Tuare is kidnapped
by Eight Fingers.
It is unacceptable for
anyone under the protection
of Ains Ooal Gown to be hurt.
Sebas ventures to a
known Eight Fingers base,
where he encounters the
group's enforcers, Six Arms.
They plan to make an example
out of him, with his execution.
Chapter Eleven: "Jaldabaoth."
Fools cannot see the truth.