[aircraft noise]
♪
[COPILOT] The left engine
block has fallen away!
We won't make it. It's over!
Don't you dare give up now!
There must be
something that we can do!
[worried chatter]
[grunts]
♪
[FEMALE REPORTER A]
You're now seeing footage from
the 23rd School
District of Academy City,
where the space plane
Orion has crash-landed.
The Orion appears to
have hit some debris
in the stratosphere
just before making re-entry.
The resulting engine
failure sent the space plane
plummeting to
the earth's surface.
[FEMALE REPORTER A] I am
thrilled and amazed to report,
however, that all
eighty-eight passengers
miraculously
survived tonight's crash.
Let me say that one more time.
All eighty-eight
passengers aboard the Orion
are confirmed to
have survived the crash.
[police siren]
[distant helicopter]
♪
[KAMIJO] Auh! Can't you just
settle for a hamburger, Index?
As a matter
of fact, I can't.
I was absolutely,
positively starving last night,
and what did
you do about it?
I'm sorry I forgot.
[grunts]
Honestly,
forgetting about supper?
How does that happen?
It's like forgetting to
take a breath or pump
blood through your veins!
Sphinx! You agree, right?
[meows]
Uh... Okay, fine. I give up.
I know when I'm outnumbered.
You can eat as
much as you want.
I won't stop you.
All I can eat?
You really mean it?
[KAMIJO] Yep and I
never go back on my word.
Hey, Toma. Did you
see that marquee?
What's a space elevator, anyw--
[SPHINX meows]
[INDEX] Ugh!
What did you do that for?
[KAMIJO] Tell me something.
You're supposed to have
a perfect memory, right?
So why are you asking?
[INDEX] Huh?
Take a look over there!
[KAMIJO] That is
a space elevator!
[gasps in awe]
Okay, I see it now.
That's strange.
Has it always been there?
Yes, of course it has!
Man you are really lost
when it comes to
science, aren't you?
[KAMIJO] Remember that time?
And that time? And that time?
And, what d'ya know,
there it is now,
right in front
of your face!
That's amazing!
I honestly had no idea.
[KAMIJO] They say the
speed at which the elevator
was constructed would
have been impossible
outside of Academy City.
[INDEX] I can see it's an
incredible piece of machinery,
but tell me something.
[KAMIJO] Sure. What?
What the heck is a
space elevator, anyway?
Let's see.
How should I explain?
It's an elevator that
can lift things into space.
What makes it special
is that it doesn't require
anything like a
rocket or a shuttle.
[INDEX] Oh! I see now!
It's like the scientific
community's response to
the Tower of Babel, huh?
Oooh...
[distant music]
Huh?
[commotion]
Let's move up a
little closer, okay?
You can see a
lot better from here.
♪ Flying so high,
dear Pegasus ♪
♪ Gloria will come to you ♪
♪ All the footprints you
had left behind are gone ♪
♪ They vanished
because of the rainfall ♪
♪ Your familiar voice and
all the kindness you'd shown ♪
♪ Will live on, when you
become one with the stars ♪
♪ Just wait
until the summertime ♪
[MIKOTO] The Miracle of
the Eighty-Eight, huh?
Yeah. I think I remember
that happening.
A while ago, right?
[UIHARU] It's been
three years now.
Immediately after
the Orion crashed,
the entire space plane program
was frozen indefinitely.
Construction on the
space elevator went into
[UIHARU] full-swing and
has been going ever since!
[MIKOTO] Yeah?
[UIHARU] I just think
it's so incredible!
The first space elevator
in the entire world.
[UIHARU] It would have
been several times--
no, several dozen times easier
to build it at the equator,
but instead they did it
right here in Academy City!
Tell me that's not impressive!
And in spite of
all the obstacles,
it's finally been completed!
Endymion is a reality!
It rises into the heavens,
the first of its kind,
a bridge between
Earth and sky!
Isn't that the most
beautiful thing ever?
Yeah, it's really great.
So, Saten, what's up?
Um. Can you even hear me?
What are you listening to?
Oh.
I'm sorry. This is Arisa.
She's an artist who streams
a lot of her stuff online.
She does a bunch of
street concerts, too.
She's so freakin'
popular right now!
I downloaded her
stuff to give her a try,
and all of her songs
are really awesome!
A new urban legend
has even sprung up.
They say if you listen
to Arisa's songs enough,
good things are more
likely to happen to you.
[MIKOTO] Oh, really?
Give it a try.
Go on, you should really
listen to her for yourself.
[MIKOTO] Uh, okay.
♪ To future generations ♪
--♪ Taking breath as you... ♪
--Huh?
Wait, I know this song.
Here! This is
her, isn't it?
♪ Sound flashes out
like a spark of light ♪
♪ World vibrations... ♪
Yeah, no doubt
about it. That's her.
Whoa! Hold on, Misaka!
Don't tell me you
actually know Arisa?
Oh, um, I, uh...
[MIKOTO chuckles]
[KUROKO growls]
I came for you, Sissy!
[UIHARU screams]
Hey, what the--?
Kuroko!
Explain yourself at once!
Exactly what are
you doing in here?
Uh. What about you?
Aren't you still supposed
to be in the hospital?
[yells]
Situations like this one are
the reason I had to get out!
[KUROKO] You know, I was
going to surprise you
by getting an early discharge.
Imagine my surprise to
find you here like this instead!
I can see I'm going
to have to take matters
into my own hands!
Bombs... away!
[groans]
Uh...
[SATEN] Uh, Shirai...
Please calm down.
[MIKOTO] I'm not doing anything!
Get off of me!
[KUROKO] You're mine! Every last
inch of you belongs to me!
[MIKOTO] Seriously, stop this!
[KUROKO] Oh Sissy!
[MIKOTO] Get away!
[CROWD gasps]
♪
[CROWD clapping]
[CROWD cheering]
[ARISA] Thank you all
so much for listening!
[INDEX clapping]
[laughing]
[giggles]
[ARISA] Thanks a lot.
I'm Arisa Meigo.
[ARISA] Uh--ah! Ahhh!
[KAMIJO grunts]
[thud]
[ARISA and KAMIJO grunt]
[groans]
[ARISA] Oh. Sorry about that.
Toma...!
[KAMIJO yells]
[INDEX] Wow! That
song was so amazing!
It was really wonderful!
You think so, too, don't ya?
To be honest with you,
I don't actually listen to
a whole lot of music.
But, even I could tell
that it was incredible,
so that's saying something!
Mhmmm!
See? It's my cell phone.
I downloaded all your songs.
Wow, thank you. I'm
so glad you like them.
I don't know what to say.
Uh-huh! You know,
I'm pretty picky when
it comes to what I listen to.
And, I know your
stuff is the real deal.
You aren't even casting
any spells over your music,
and it still charms the pants
off of everyone who hears it!
Casting spells?
Well, yeah, you know,
everything in your song
just comes across
so clearly. Right!
For a second I thought it
was telepathy or something.
But I guess that's not it, huh?
[chuckles]
No, unfortunately not.
I'm a Level 0,
so that's impossible.
Huh? You're a Level Zero?
[ARISA] Mm-hmm. For a long time
it really bothered me a lot,
but now I'm kinda
grateful, you know?
Grateful?
It sounds weird,
but if I had an ability,
I'm sure that's what
I would be focusing on.
That would be my passion.
I doubt I ever would
have started singing.
[INDEX] Hm?
You really think so?
Mmm.
I know so! I was never
good at school or sports.
The only thing I ever
had any kind of talent
for at all was singing.
So I made up my mind.
I'd do whatever it
takes to become a singer!
That's my dream. To be
a real singer, to perform
in front of a huge
audience on a big stage.
You could say it's what
I want more than anything!
Ow! Too bright!
She's shining so much,
she's gonna blind me!
[INDEX] I think my
eyeballs are burning!
[cell phone ringing]
[ARISA gasps]
Um, do you mind if I?
[INDEX and KAMIJO] Mmm.
[ARISA] Hello?
Yes, this is she. Yes.
What? Wait, are
you serious? Oh!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Yes! Right!
I understand.
[ARISA] I had an audition.
[BOTH] Huh?
And whadaya know...
That was them calling.
I'm gonn get my big debut!
[ARISA laughing]
[KAMIJO] Wow! That's really
amazing! A real gig!
Does that mean
you're gonna be on TV?
[INDEX] Huh? TV?
[giggles]
I didn't realize you'd be just
like Kanamin! This is amazing!
[ARISA] Kanamin?
[INDEX] We absolutely
have to celebrate!
[ARISA] Oh, okay.
[INDEX] I know! We'll go have
a fancy dinner in your honor.
Sky's the limit!
[KAMIJO] Wha--?!
What do you say?
Will you eat with us?
I, uh. I don't know.
It's our
treat right, Toma?
[KAMIJO sighs]
[KAMIJO] So... this audition,
does it have anything
to do with Endymion?
[ARISA] Yeah. How did you
guess? They chose my song
to be the theme for
the Endymion campaign.
[INDEX]
Hey, I know what that is!
It's an elevator
that goes into space.
Arisa, are you
going into space, too?
[ARISA] I'm still not
sure about that, actually.
It does sound like
there's going to be
an opening ceremony, though.
[INDEX giggles]
--[INDEX] Excuse me! I'll take
--[KAMIJO] Enough!
--an order of fried oysters--
--Take pity on me!
[INDEX exhales heavily]
Your wish is really
coming true, huh?
You must be so happy.
Mhmmm.
It may sound strange,
but I've always had
good luck like that.
I know this only happened...
because I'm a
really lucky girl.
C'mon give
yourself some credit.
Huh?
Success isn't about luck.
You have to be willing
to get out there.
To stand in the batter's box.
[KAMIJO] To swing
for all you're worth,
hoping you'll
get a good hit!
[KAMIJO] Or not.
I hate to tell you, but
that wasn't very convincing.
Is there more?
'Kay, fine. Luck as bad as mine
does sometimes come into play.
[KAMIJO] But that's
not true for you.
You were chosen for your talent.
And personally,
I think that's something
you can be really proud of.
You're so sweet.
Uh! Hey! Look out!
[ARISA sighs]
I can't remember the
last time I had so much fun!
Thanks a lot. It was really
nice hanging out with
the two of you
for the entire day.
[panting]
Hey, you know. I'm
actually a Level 0, too.
[KAMIJO] So I guess that
makes it extra inspiring to me
when somebody's
dream comes true.
You're making me blush!
He's not alone, though.
I love seeing someone
work so hard
for their future.
It really motivates me.
Yeah, I know!
Doesn't it make you
wanna shoot for the stars?
[INDEX] Yes! Wait!
That doesn't sound right!
I already have a noble
calling, thank you very much.
I'm a Sister!
Should I take your casual
dismissal of that fact
as an insult to the
entire English Church?
[KAMIJO] Calm down! That's
not what I meant at all!
I was talking about
something more personal.
Like helping out with
the housework, for example.
[INDEX] Shut up!
I eat, you clean.
That's how it works.
[KAMIJO] Well, it
doesn't work for me!
I mean, how can you
be a nun and a glutton?
Listen.
[ARISA singing a melody]
[singing continues]
That was a beautiful
melody, Arisa.
I really enjoyed it.
Hey, I've heard that.
In fact, it's one of the
songs I downloaded earlier.
[ARISA giggles]
[KAMIJO]
Does it have any lyrics?
[ARISA] No, not yet.
I'm still working on them.
Thank you again.
I had a wonderful time.
I can let you guys
know when my concert
is going to be,
if you'd like to come.
Sounds good.
We can't wait to
see you perform.
♪
I call on Undine by
the symbol of the chalice.
That which is distilled
from all things.
Uh...!
[ALL gasp]
[ARISA] Whoa! What's that?
[BOTH] Uh!
What's happening?
[INDEX] Be careful, Toma!
[gasps]
[INDEX] It's a spell that
calls upon a water element.
♪
And that means these are
magicians we're up against.
[ALL] Ah!
I want both of you
to stay back, okay?
You're up Marybeth!
Slow him down for me!
Ugh! The ground!
Jane! Now!
♪
[JANE gasps]
[KAMIJO] What do you want
with us? Who are you people?
[screams]
What happened? Was
that Spell Intercept?
Yaaa!
Uh--!
Wait, is that--?
[MARYBETH coughing]
Thanks, Master.
Why did you
act on your own?
I told you to wait
for my order, didn't I?
Mmm.
[running footsteps]
[KAMIJO] It is you!
What the hell, Stiyl?
What are you doing here?
Move it, kid. Fortis 931!
Your magic name?
Are you serious?
♪
What are you
three waiting for?
[STIYL] Seize the girl!
[KAMIJO] Arisa!
Ah!
Your right hand's powerful.
[STIYL] But it
can't destroy matter.
Look out, Toma!
[ARISA] Stop this!
No!
What just happened?
[gasps]
What the hell?
♪
[beeping]
Go!
[INDEX and KAMIJO] Ahh!
♪
[STIYL grunts]
[KAMIJO grunts]
What is that thing?
[WOMAN] Attention! We are
the Civil Conflict Resolution
and Relief Patrol.
We're authorized by
the city's governing board.
Be advised. This is
a special intervention.
♪
[GIRL grunts]
[STIYL] Ugh...
Tch. Uh...
♪
[STIYL grunts]
Come on, Styil. We're going
to have to get a handle
on this situation quickly,
or there'll be trouble.
Tch.
Well, ladies. You heard
what she said. Move out now.
[ALL] Right!
♪
[KANZAKI] What else can you do?
[KAMIJO] Hey, hold on!
Why are you after Arisa?
[GIRLS panting]
[STIYL] She's more
important than you know.
The girl could start a war,
between the scientific
and magic communities.
What? A war?
Hey! Care to elaborate?
Auhhh...
What do you want?
Who are you?
As I was trying to
explain to you before,
we are a specialized
task force charged with
[WOMAN] maintaining
order in Academy City.
[KAMIJO] That doesn't
tell me what I need to know.
Are you trying to hurt
that girl over there
or are you on her side?
[WOMAN] The combat we
just went through was part of
our commissioned duty as
Civil Relief Patrol members.
[KAMIJO] That doesn't
answer my question!
Hm. I'm warning you now.
Do not become
involved with her.
Because if you do,
then chances are...
[WOMAN] you will die.
[grunts]
♪ [ARISA'S melody] ♪
[gasps]
[INDEX] Hm?
Have a bad dream?
Oh, are you awake now?
Um. Where am I?
[INDEX] We brought you home.
Welcome to Toma's place.
[KAMIJO] This isn't my home!
Uh, what I mean is,
this is just a dorm
the school provides.
Oh, okay.
Did you recognize any of
those people we saw earlier?
[KAMIJO] Maybe you've
bumped in to them before?
Mm-mmm.
Mhmmm!
It makes sense that she
wouldn't recognize them.
After all, they were magi--
Yeah, they were, majorly,
um, majorly powerful
in some way that can't possibly
be explained by science alone.
Wait, do you believe
in it, too, Toma?
I, um, believe in what?
[INDEX grumbling]
Well, it's like--you know...
Like a strange,
mysterious sort of power
that can't be
understood by science.
I don't know about you,
but I've always found
esper abilities to
be pretty mysterious.
[breathing heavily]
[growls]
Oh, uh. I'm sorry.
Don't kill me.
Anyway. Arisa, are you
saying that you wish
there was such a power?
[ARISA] Well, actually.
I'm saying I have that power.
[INDEX and KAMIJO] Huh?
[ARISA] It happens
when I'm singing.
It sounds crazy, but
it's true. I swear it is.
When I sing, it's like I have
some unquantifiable power.
They examine me regularly
at Kirigaoka Academy,
where I go to
school, but no luck.
Even they don't seem to
have any idea what it is.
I can't help but wonder if
this power is the only reason
that people listen to my songs.
As much as I hate to think so,
it's totally possible.
[KAMIJO] No way!
If that were the case,
then my right hand would--
--[KAMIJO] I, uh.
--[INDEX] Listen to him.
He's right for once.
Your songs are the real deal.
[SPHINX meows]
[meows]
Thank you.
[ARISA] It may sound silly,
but I wanted to make
everyone happy with my songs.
I knew that if I was making
other people happy,
then I would be happy, too.
[ARISA] But now,
if anyone were to get hurt
because of my songs, then...
Don't say that. You can't
think about backing out now.
Not after they've
accepted your audition.
What I'm trying
to say is,
ultimately, singing is just
a selfish desire of mine.
What if people come after
me like they did before?
It could be worse this time.
They could hurt
somebody close to me.
So that's it?
You're giving up.
You're going to
sacrifice your dream because
somebody came along and
intimidated you with force?
Mmm.
Honestly. What do you
want more than anything?
[ARISA] I want to sing.
It's all I have.
It's what I love,
what I'm passionate about.
[meows]
[KAMIJO] Then go ahead and sing.
Singing is what you love to do,
and you really
have a gift for it.
You can't give it up.
We'll just have to
come up with a plan.
A way to keep you out
of danger while you sing.
Thanks!
In that case,
I guess that you'll be
staying here for a while.
Huh?
After what happened before,
the magicians aren't
likely to make any
moves in public.
And if Arisa's here at the dorm,
then we'll be
around to protect her.
Well, what do you think?
Magicians?
[KAMIJO] Aah!
She means the enemy!
As long as you're here,
they'll leave you alone!
[laughs nervously]
You don't mind?
[KAMIJO exhales heavily]
It does seem like the
most logical solution.
Okay, this'll be no problem.
A guy, two girls, and a cat.
The more the merrier!
Please, come in.
It's a pleasure to welcome
you to my humble home.
[INDEX and ARISA giggle]
[WOMAN] Yes.
The enemy used abilities
that are yet undetermined.
[GIRL]
Undetermined, you say?
I guess these days people
can do all sorts of things
they weren't able to before.
Especially in this city.
[WOMAN]
This is different, though.
I believe they possess power
that's particularly unusual.
[GIRL] Now, now is that
of any real significance
to someone such as yourself,
who possesses an
unusual power of her own?
You wouldn't be
worried, would you?
[WOMAN] I don't mean
unusual simply in terms of
being few in number.
Arisa Meigo was attacked.
Exactly as you
said she would be.
So, who am I dealing with here?
Why do you ask?
You can fight without
knowing the answer.
[SHUTAURA sighs]
And another thing.
Are you entirely certain
that this line is secure?
[SHUTAURA] I'm hearing
something in the background.
Hearing something? Ah!
Oh, yes, I think
I know what you mean.
[music playing]
[gasps]
[LADYLEE] How's that? Is the
line quiet enough for you now?
Yes, it is.
Very good.
Now, where were we?
[LADYLEE] Ah, yes,
if you would please
escort her again tomorrow.
Understood.
[outside traffic]
[PIERCE] Okay, Kami, listen up!
You're a groupie now,
and you picked a great time
to become one. You're getting
in on the ground floor!
[PIERCE] That's the
way to do it, man.
Chicks like Arisa get famous
quicker than you'd think.
Take your eyes off her
for a second and bam!
She's a rock star and
you're left eating her dust.
I'm tellin' ya,
these days you really
have to make every minute count!
"Seize the day" and what not?
Hmmm.
What's with you?
You seem more
exhausted than usual.
Yeah, I didn't
get any sleep.
[KAMIJO] I've got another
guest crashing at my place.
Between the two of
them, they've stolen
all my pillows and blankets.
[HIMEGAMI] He's not
getting enough sleep.
And the blankets, he's fighting
for control of the blankets.
What's the matter?
[KOMOE] Okay, everybody!
Let's quiet down
and take our seats, please!
Class is starting.
It's time to learn!
[KOMOE] Kamijo, you look like
you've been hit by a truck.
Did you get any rest
at all last night?
A growing body like yours needs
plenty of sleep, young man!
Yeah? Then can I take a nap?
No, I'm afraid not, Kamijo.
[KOMOE] And, for
asking that, you get to
take a remedial class!
Ahhh!
We'll get through
it together, okay?
[KOMOE] So don't you worry!
[running water]
[INDEX] It's really annoying.
Toma treats me like a child
instead of a young lady!
I know why. It's because
you're such a little cutie.
He can't help himself!
[INDEX] Huh?
Did you say something?
Mmm...
So, given the circumstances,
I should ask.
The relationship
that you have with Toma...
How would you define it?
Hm?
Well, Toma does the
shopping and makes food.
I look cute and eat food.
And, whenever I
get myself into trouble,
he's always there to
help me get out of it again.
Despite how he looks,
Toma's actually
a pretty incredible guy
when you get to know him.
Mmhmmm!
[ARISA] A nun and a Level 0
does seem kinda strange.
But, ya know, you
guys are pretty cool.
Arisa?
What are you doing?
[INDEX] Is something the matter?
One sec, okay? I just need
to jot down these lyrics.
[INDEX] Lyrics? Really?
So that's how you
write a song, then!
Lemme see! Lemme see!
[ARISA] I can't.
It's too embarrassing.
[INDEX] Huh? No fair!
I wanna see! Pretty please!
[ARISA] I'll show
you when I'm done.
Then we can sing
it together. Okay?
[INDEX giggles]
Yeah! You have a deal!
You swear?
No take backs!
Hey, I'm ho--ah!
[KAMIJO] Ah...!
Uh, Toma!
You're in trouble now!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[KAMIJO] Stupid, rotten luck!
[KAMIJO] Tomorrow?
Yep. I'm discussing
my contract
with the Orbit
Portal people.
Oh, really?
It's just,
I've got a remedial
class to go to.
I don't think there's
any possible way
I could make it
there in time.
[KAMIJO] I can't
entrust Index with this.
That would only
make me worry more.
Is there anybody else?
A good friend, maybe?
Someone you could ask to
go with you just this once?
Mmm...
[MIKOTO]
Hello! Sorry we're late!
[MIKOTO] Yeah? You mean Orbit
Portal is the same company
that was responsible for the
Orion incident three years ago?
[UIHARU] Yes. They staked
the fate of the company
on the space plane
project and would have
gone bankrupt after the crash.
But then they were bought out
and experienced a
miraculous recovery.
That's when work
on Endymion took off,
and, well, the rest is history!
Okay...
Oh, and you
know what else?
The president of the company
is actually a young girl!
She's only about ten years old
now, if I remember correctly.
Huh? You mean when
the buyout happened,
she was only
seven years old?
She is nothing more
than a figurehead
for the company,
though, isn't she?
I mean, a munchkin beauty
queen in charge of everything?
Who would take
her seriously?
I hear she's
pretty weird, too.
You think so, Shirai?
As weird as a beat-up,
pig-tailed, teleporter
in a wheelchair?
Uh!
[KUROKO] Uiharu!
[chuckles nervously]
[ding]
So, I've got another
urban legend for you guys.
Supposedly, this child-president
of theirs is really just
a promotional hologram
or a robot or something.
Least, that's
the rumor, anyway.
Ha! Definitely
an urban legend.
C'mon, there could
be some truth to it.
You never know. I mean,
have you ever seen her?
[SATEN] She really looks like a
little porcelain doll sometimes.
Why did you stop? Is
there something the matter?
No, this doll just
looks so much like...
[gasp]
I like your songs.
They're pretty.
[LADYLEE] Which is surprising,
I can't think of a singer
I've liked since Jenny Lind.
I wish you good luck.
That was her.
[ALL gasp]
[PRODUCTION CREW commotion]
[ARISA] Hi, I'm Arisa.
Nice to meet all of you.
--[MAN A] What's goin' on?
--[MAN B] How are you?
[MAN C] Glad you could make it.
Hey!
[ARISA] I'm really
looking forward to this!
[FEMALE DIRECTOR]
Oh? And who are these folks?
Oh. Uh,
I'm Arisa's manager.
Nice to meet you.
Hmm. Hmm...
You'll make for passable
stage decorations.
Uuuh...
[music begins]
[FEMALE DIRECTOR] Okay!
Let's get this show started!
[camera flashes]
[music continues]
[laughing nervously]
Sorry about this.
I didn't realize that we
would be getting so involved.
I'm so nervous I feel
sick. But exited!
And, I get to go
shake the money maker.
[KUROKO] Come on! Hurry up
and get out there, already!
I--I don't know.
Don't be shy, Saten!
The stage is this way!
[camera flashes]
[MIKOTO sighs]
Hey, what's Zapper
doing down there?
[KAMIJO] As long as she's here
there's nothing to worry about.
Isn't that the lady
from the other night?
[ARISA'S song plays] ♪ ...side
on this familiar path ♪
[music muffled]
[door opens]
Uh!
[music stops]
[electical power shuts off]
[MALE ONLOOKER A]
What's wrong? A power outage?
[FEMALE ONLOOKER A] Oh, no!
[SHUTAURA] You should
know that Arisa Meigo is
under the protection
of the Black Crow Force.
♪
[gasps]
Ah!
Ugh...
[running footsteps]
Him again?
[KAMIJO yells]
[radio static]
[CROW 7] Crow 7 to Crow Leader.
What is it?
Explosives located on
D Block. Several of them.
[SHUTAURA]
Evacuate immediately!
All other units,
get the target away fro--
♪
[grunts]
[yells]
♪
[gasps]
[KAMIJO groans]
[glass shattering]
[ARISA, SATEN,
and UIHARU whimper]
An explosion?
Kuroko!
[KUROKO] Got it!
Come on, let's go.
[rumbling]
[grunts]
This place is crumbling!
♪
[MAN A coughs]
[MAN A] Is everyone alright?
Listen! Judgment
is here to help you!
Just call out if
you need assistance!
[MAN B coughs]
Are you okay, man?
Yeah, thanks.
[MALE ONLOOKER B]
That was really close.
[FEMALE ONLOOKER B]
We all could have died!
[MALE ONLOOKER C] If that had
fallen a little to the left.
[FEMALE ONLOOKER C]
It really is a miracle!
[MALE ONLOOKER D]
Yeah, it's a miracle!
[MALE ONLOOKER E] A miracle!
[water drops]
Mmm.
Uuuh...
Wake up! Get off me,
will you? Come on!
[SHUTAURA] Meigo wasn't
harmed at all? How many dead?
What do you mean none?
Very well. Carry on, then.
[beeps]
[KAMIJO groans]
[SHUTAURA]
Are you finally awake?
Where are we?
[whimpers]
Don't move
around too much.
[KAMIJO] Wait, are they okay?
Arisa and the others?
They're safe.
Your friend
is just fine,
and so are all
the spectators.
And what about the
rest of your people?
They're all right, too.
The Black Crow Force
got through this
without any injury.
Wow, that really is
miraculous, isn't it?
[groans]
Do not speak that
word in my presence.
Do you understand me?
[SHUTAURA] Things just
happened to work out well.
There's nothing
more to it than that.
Nothing more
special than a random
quantum mechanical deviation.
That and people's
irrational need
to sensationalize
a happy ending.
[coughing]
Humans have grown
indolent and foolish.
Always waiting for
some great "unseen hand"
to swoop in and save them.
I get it. You lead
men into combat.
That means you have to
maintain a tough exterior,
but Arisa, she is
the real thing.
Have you listened
to her songs before?
You should really
give them a try sometime.
They might even make someone
like you believe in miracles.
[SHUTAURA] I was in an
accident. Because of that,
my brain has lost the
ability to recognize music.
[gasps]
[SHUTAURA] I can
hear spoken words fine,
but my brain can't process
rhythm and changes in pitch.
Which means no music.
Where I'm concerned,
a song is nothing but
noise assaulting my ears.
[sighs]
[KAMIJO] I'm sorry.
What was your na--
[SHUTAURA] I'm Shutaura.
Shutaura Sequenzia.
[KAMIJO] I'm sorry,
Shutaura, really.
[SHUTAURA] Why apologize?
I'm perfectly content
with the way things are.
[SHUTAURA] I'm never
swayed by popular music,
and I don't jump on bandwagons
or get distracted by
so-called "miracles."
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER A] We will
now continue our live coverage
of the bombing at the 7th
School District shopping mall.
There have been
reports of an explosion
in the facility
underneath the mall,
but the exact cause is
still under investigation.
The city is shaken.
At the time of the bombing,
a live event was underway
for the singer Arisa,
and yet there was not
a single fatality reported.
[MAN C] It's a miracle.
A real miracle!
[YOUNG GIRL A]
They say it was a miracle.
[YOUNG GIRL B]
Yeah, a miracle!
[WOMAN A] A miracle?
[MAN C]
Arisa is a miracle maker!
[WOMAN A] It's a miracle!
[MAN C] A miracle!
[CROWD chatter]
[footsteps]
[KAMIJO] Are you all right?
Huh?
[ARISA] Toma.
[ARISA] It doesn't
seem right, does it?
I mean, if it
really was a miracle...
well, wouldn't
the whole incident
never have happened
in the first place?
You know, you
might have a point.
[ARISA] This could be
turning into a pattern.
Apparently I was
involved in another
potentially
catastrophic accident.
"Apparently"?
I know it's strange, but
I don't have any memories
before three years ago.
[gasps]
My name was given to
me by someone who was
working for the facility that
took me in after the accident.
[ARISA] So, I don't have
anything that I can call my own.
But when I'm singing, I don't
care about any of that.
I know exactly who I am.
And then I don't
feel so lonely anymore.
As long as I have my
songs, I feel like I can
recover what I lost. Like
someday I'll be whole again.
I understand what you're
going through more than
you may realize. And I
think you're really lucky
to have something you
believe in so passionately.
[KAMIJO] Don't worry.
It'll turn out all right.
[FEMALE INTERVIEWER]
Endymion's unveiling ceremony
is coming up in two days,
isn't that right?
Yes. We are more than
ready to show the results
of our years of hard work.
[LADYLEE] I have no doubt that
our company will once again
help the world see what
a true miracle looks like!
[cheering]
[music begins]
[music continues]
♪ Softly, as though
it were a prayer ♪
♪ I take words and
spin them together ♪
♪ and string them together ♪
♪ Into stories to
be told... someday ♪
♪ Right now, I'm
starting to believe ♪
♪ that I can tell you ♪
♪ The way that I
feel when you are near ♪
♪ I'm finally
brave enough to say ♪
♪ The moment when my dreams
and reality finally are one ♪
♪ My wish is coming true now ♪
♪ Could it be that miracles
are happening all around? ♪
[LADYLEE] A miraculous
singing voice.
Without it, she's
unremarkable, but with it,
I believe she has the power
and influence of a true star.
Wouldn't you agree?
No. It all sounds
like noise to me,
and I don't
believe in miracles.
You know, you have a
very unpleasant disposition.
[LADYLEE] There is one thing
and one thing only that has
kept Orbit Portal
thriving instead of crashing
into the ground
like the Orion did,
and that is the legend of
the Miracle of the Eighty-eight.
In a sense, miracles are our
company's greatest commodity.
What happened on the Orion
was by no means a miracle--
A plane fell from outer space,
and eighty-eight
people survived.
[LADYLEE] If that isn't a
miracle, then what is it?
[ARISA'S song continues]
It won't be long now.
Everything is in order.
[LADYLEE] All of our
preparations are complete.
It's almost time.
Are you ready?
Mhmm.
I want to thank
you for helping me.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Today is my treat,
so order whatever you want.
Anything at all!
[INDEX] Really?
Oh, waitress! Over here!
Sure, coming!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Wow! A girl
like her? A budding pop star?
Only you, Kami, only you.
[KAMIJO] Don't play dumb
with me, Tsuchimikado.
I want some honest
answers from you.
Tell me why
Arisa's being targeted.
[KANZAKI] That's simple.
She's a saint.
Or she's said to have
power comparable to one,
at any rate, and that's
enough to make her interesting.
[KAMIJO] Kanzaki!
[KANZAKI] She's provisionally
ranked ninth, but if she was
to come into her full power,
there's a decent chance
that she would be
even stronger than I am.
[KAMIJO] Arisa Meigo's a saint?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] That's
still just supposition.
Call it our working theory.
But nothing has
actually been proven yet.
[KANZAKI] Well, what about you?
What's your opinion on it?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
I'm not entirely sure.
Defining saints is always
such an imprecise business.
It might help the
process if I could
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
give you a thorough exam.
Every last inch of you.
Absolutely not!
Stay away from me!
Well, whether Arisa's a saint
or not, one thing is clear.
There are people in the
city who want to analyze
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
whatever gifts she has
and find a way to exploit them.
Particularly that lolita
in charge of Orbit Portal.
[ARISA] Here.
Hm?
The lyrics
to that song.
I promised we'd sing
them together, didn't I?
[gasps in awe]
I think this deserves
a toast, so here's to you!
Here's to you!
[BOTH] Cheers!
[chuckles]
Wow! The three-
legged race, really?
And with a partner
like Misaka, too!
What can I say, she
insisted on running with me,
and I couldn't very well
turn her down, could I?
[ALL gasp]
[WANNAI] Who're they?
Yes. Explain yourselves!
[GIRLS scream]
[mumbles]
Huh? I didn't catch that.
[phone vibrates]
Why is she calling me?
Uh, what is it, Index?
[KAMIJO] What? Arisa?
[SHUTAURA] Come in Crow 4,
this is Crow Leader. Sitrep.
[CROW 4] Currently pursuing
target on the expressway.
[SHUTAURA] Don't lose them.
[SHUTAURA] There's no
such thing as a miracle.
And I'm going to prove it.
[car horn honks]
[JANE] Um, excuse me, Master?
[STIYL] Hmm?
You really shouldn't be
smoking that inside the car.
[JANE] It results
in stunted growth.
Doesn't really matter to me.
I'm already
plenty tall as it is.
I don't mean you!
I'm talking about me!
[gasps]
They're here!
Marye, don't let
them pass us!
Got it, sir!
♪
[beeping]
[MARYE, JANE,
and MARYBETH scream]
[ALL scream]
[STIYL grunts]
Uh!
[JANE] Master!
Use these!
[STIYL] Innocentius, strike!
Uh!
[roaring]
[CROW 4 yells]
[beep]
They're just up ahead!
Can't this thing
go any faster?
I'm trying!
I promise I'm trying!
[distant explosion]
♪
[STIYL gasps]
[car tires screech]
[MARYE] Whew.
[MALLYBATH] Ugh.
[JANE] Owie.
Stop this, Styil!
[KAMIJO] You're jumping
the gun here, and you know it!
There's still no proof
that she's a saint,
so why don't you
just leave her alone?
[sighs]
Thanks, Kanzaki.
[STIYL] I have recently been
given a new set of orders.
You know what that
thing over there is?
Yeah, of course.
It's a space elevator.
[STIYL] Nope.
Consider the Sumerian
ziggurats, the Tower of Babel.
When structures are
built on a scale that
exceeds the very
bounds of rationality,
they take on magical
properties, as well.
And you know what happens when
some evil mastermind
gets a saint involved?
[STIYL] The structure
in question can become
a large-scale
magical instrument.
[KAMIJO] Hold on a second!
Are you saying there's someone
in Academy City who's
trying to use magic?
Uh.
[LADYLEE] It's me. Antiskill
is on the move. Withdraw now.
[SHUTAURA] Roger.
[SHUTAURA gasps]
It can't be. That's impossible!
[LADYLEE] Oh, dear. Found out
about that, have we? Alright.
Bring the girl back here
at once. We'll have a chat.
[SHUTAURA] Stay back!
[KAMIJO] Shutaura!
You don't have to do this!
Please, let her go!
This isn't your business!
[SHUTAURA] So why
are you interfering?
That's not good.
Get out of here! Now!
[KAMIJO yells]
[keyboard clicking]
[sighs]
[cell phone ringing]
[MIKOTO] Saten's calling?
[MIKOTO] Hello, Saten.
Yeah, what's up? Uh huh, yeah.
What's that? Arisa's missing?
Yeah. They don't know
where she might be.
They're pretty certain
she's been abducted.
[MIKOTO] Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm. Alright, got it.
I'm heading out now.
[beep]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps]
[SHUTAURA] Who is this girl?
And what in the world is
she doing with this bracelet?
[door opens]
[LADYLEE] It's as I assumed.
You two are drawn
to one another.
On the day that the
Orion crashed to the Earth
there were eighty-eight
passengers and crew aboard.
[LADYLEE] When they
counted after the accident
they confirmed that there
were eighty-eight survivors.
It was truly a miracle.
Everyone said so.
But the truth is, there
was a single fatality.
The pilot of the Orion.
Daedalus Sequenzia.
That's right.
Your father died that day.
But, by the time his demise
was officially confirmed,
it was already too late.
The world was caught
up in the miracle.
[LADYLEE] So it was never
revealed that there were
actually eighty-nine
people on the plane
when it came crashing down.
There were only eighty-eight
when the plane took off,
but one girl appeared
suddenly in transit.
She appeared, and then
she worked a miracle.
[LADYLEE] This is that girl.
[SHUTAURA] Must you persist in
calling the accident a miracle?
[LADYLEE] You know, the way
that "accident" was designed,
nobody should have survived.
[SHUTAURA gasps]
What're you saying?
I was so confident. I thought
for sure that it would work.
[LADYLEE] However,
except for your father,
every single person lived.
Fortunately, it did produce an
especially useful by-product.
So in that sense,
I suppose it was a success.
[SHUTAURA]
The crash, it was you.
[SHUTAURA] You did this!
[grunting]
Uh...!
[panting]
[SHUTAURA] Who are you, girl?
♪
[LADYLEE chuckles]
[gasps]
[SHUTAURA] You're that,
guy from before!
[SHUTAURA struggling]
[LADYLEE] Are you finished
with your tantrum?
By my last count,
that's the sixteenth time
I've been stabbed now.
You're a monster.
Well, you could call me that.
I'm not an ordinary human,
that much is certain.
[LADYLEE] But then again,
neither are the two of you.
Which is why I'm
going to let you live.
[LADYLEE] I know how
you love miracles.
Be patient and you'll
see yet another one.
Whoever you are and whatever
it is you're planning,
I swear that I will stop
you! I swear, you hear me?
Yes, I look forward
to it. Take her away.
Now then, girl.
That just leaves you and me.
[LADYLEE] Good morning.
There's a little
favor I need from you,
if it's not too much trouble.
[cheering]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER A]
Those with ticket numbers
two-zero-three-three
through two-one-five-two
please embark on the
Number Seventeen linear track.
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER B]
The much-anticipated unveiling
ceremony is
scheduled for tomorrow.
Accordingly, excited
guests have been rolling
in non-stop all day.
I don't believe it.
Are you sure?
Yeah. There's no sign of her.
She never came back.
I did some looking around,
too, but I came up empty.
Where is she?
--[MIKOTO] Well...
--[INDEX] Toma.
Hmm.
Wha... Huh...?
My goodness.
Injured again, are you?
[FROG DOCTOR]
You're trying to set a new
hospital admittance
record, is that it?
Um, no, sir. Not exactly.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Kami! How's it goin'?
Can we borrow
you for a second?
[beeping]
Crow 7 to all units.
System infiltration
was successful.
[beeping]
[STIYL] We're going to
put an end to all this.
What are you saying?
The president,
Ladylee Tangleroad,
was originally
on our side.
She's a sybil, specializing
in Greek divination.
Unfortunately,
it seems she's gone rogue,
trying to construct a spell
with Arisa at its core.
She's using Endymion.
We're talking about
a colossal spell.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Something
with enough power
to wipe out the entire
northern hemisphere
if we allow it
to be activated.
[gasps]
So, at any rate, as long as
the problem is a magical one,
it falls within
our territory.
Which means you guys
can keep out of it.
You sure you
can handle it?
I mean it is
outer space.
We can deal with the core.
And if it's necessary,
[STIYL] we'll destroy
the tower itself.
When you say you can
"deal with the core"
do you mean you're
going to kill Arisa?
Sorry, kid. There's no choice.
[KAMIJO] You don't
know her. She has a dream.
She's poured her entire
heart into pursuing it.
Why is she being
treated like the villain,
as if she's the one
responsible for some
[KAMIJO] crazy plan
to tear the world apart?
Uh.
Toma! Stop!
[INDEX] You shouldn't be up yet!
There's no choice;
we're running out of time.
[KAMIJO] Whether by
science or by magic,
Arisa is going to be killed.
Huh?
I see he's as
big a fool as ever.
[INDEX] I'm coming, too!
We had a feeling
you'd say that,
so we got something
ready for ya.
[KAMIJO] Huh?
[MISAKA SISTERS] "Stare."
[LAST ORDER] "Yes, yes.
I see what you mean.
It sounds like this could be a
real mess in the making, huh?"
agrees Misaka Misaka,
using her best stage whisper.
[laughing]
Quiet down, will ya?
Whispers aren't supposed to
be that loud,
you know. Dumb girl.
[giggles]
[MIKOTO] Hey, thirsty?
I raided the vending machine.
Where is he?
Why that little!
[LADYLEE] A plane
fell from outer space,
and eighty-eight
people survived.
If that isn't a miracle,
then what is it?
[door opens]
[CROW 7] Sorry for the delay.
What's our status?
Ladylee's
headed into space.
The operation's
advanced to Phase 4.
[CROW 7] An Antiskill
squad is approaching
Endymion as we speak.
So are we ready to go up?
Yes, we're ready.
Are you sure, ma'am?
This is something I
need to settle myself.
Don't send anybody
else up after me.
[SHUTAURA] I'm off.
[CROWD commotion]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER B] Attention:
we are now temporarily
shutting down the
network to adjust
the relay circuits
for the ceremony.
Please wait a moment
for service to resume.
[ARISA] A miracle.
I have a very special
request to make of you.
I'd like for you to
sing your miracle song.
[ARISA] I'm sorry, Toma.
What an ungrateful
wretch you are.
[LADYLEE] If it weren't
for me, you would still be
squawking on the sidewalks.
I gave you a real
stage to perform upon.
You can always refuse
my request if you like.
Of course, the
unfortunate result of your
refusal would be the deaths of
everybody who came here today.
[ARISA] Okay. I'll sing.
But that doesn't mean you win.
I won't be singing to
make either your dream
or mine come true.
[ARISA] My song will be
dedicated to the people
who are genuinely
looking forward to it.
[ARISA] It's them
I'll be singing for.
No matter what you plan, the
miracle song will rise above it.
It's stronger than
you are. A lot stronger.
[aircraft noise]
What is this?
It's a Ballistic Slider.
It has the dubious honor
[TSUCHIMIKADO] of being the
shuttle system that lost out
as the city's next big
space transport craft.
This baby's gonna take you
all the way to outer space!
What? It's going where?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Outer space!
Keep up now, Kami.
[YOMIKAWA] What's the status of
the various underground tunnels
and payload routes?
All those paths
have been sealed off.
You know what that
means, don't you?
[YOMIKAWA] This bridge
is the only entry point
left open to us.
[cheering]
[ARISA] ♪ The stars shining
brightly and so beautifully ♪
♪ that put my mind at ease ♪
♪ Give me hope ♪
Alright, boys, let's go!
♪
♪ Many sleepless nights, ♪
♪ I'd search for
comfort up above me ♪
♪ I believed that the stars
were always listening ♪
[ARISA] ♪ But my fear
overcame the faith ♪
♪ that I once
had in happiness ♪
It's all up to you
now, man. Go get 'em.
[ARISA] ♪ The glow of my tears
that trickled down my cheeks ♪
♪ are what became ♪
--That's our cue. Let's go.
--♪ My shooting star ♪
--Yeah!
--[MARYE and MARYBETH] Yeah!
--♪ My shooting star ♪
♪ And I flick them away like
they were grains of sand ♪
♪ (The stars
twinkle in the sky) ♪
♪ But I'm not giving up hope ♪
♪ that one day I could see ♪
♪ A great light, make a wish, ♪
♪ that will finally
reach to the sky ♪
♪ If I let emotions
run so high ♪
♪ they stretch to meet
the heavens above ♪
♪ Know that my intention's
always been to wish ♪
♪ your happiness ♪
--♪ I'm one step away from... ♪
--[LADYLEE] Life and death.
Finite and infinite.
So many contrasting
concepts intersecting.
There are different
laws in space than
there are on the ground.
[LADYLEE] The fanaticism and
blood of the people will be
an offering given in a
feast to appease the gods.
Their life's breath is key!
When they all die, Endymion's
curse will be broken!
[ARISA'S song] ♪ Tonight
I'll make it come true ♪
[gasps]
Wow, look up there!
[INDEX] Amazing! I've
never seen a magic array
as big as this one!
It actually brings in the Earth
itself as part of the spell.
[KAMIJO] What happens
once it's activated?
I really can't say without
knowing what its objective is.
I do think it's
Goetian in nature,
[INDEX] but this isn't
in any of the records.
[beeping]
Uh, that sounds bad!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Hey,
travelers! How's it goin'?
Forgive the intrusion,
but I've got some
unfortunate news, uh...
The elevator's equipped
with anti-debris missiles,
and it seems
they're locked on you.
[KAMIJO] What're we supposed
to do? Do we have any weapons?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Are you
kidding? Of course!
[ARISA'S song] ♪ ...Polaris,
shining over me ♪
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Okay!
Looks like you're up!
Tsuchimikado.
I won't forget about this.
[KANZAKI grunts]
[ARISA'S song] ♪ If I let
emotions run so high ♪
♪ they stretch to meet
the heavens above ♪
♪ Know that my intention's
always been to wish ♪
♪ our happiness ♪
♪ The sky is exactly like our
dreams because to both of them ♪
♪ there is no end ♪
♪ So I let my voice ring out
and sing as loud as I can ♪
♪ I want to make
sure my emotions ♪
♪ find their way back to you. ♪
--[yells]
--♪ For ages to come ♪
[ARISA'S song] ♪ A star
in the whole sky, ♪
♪ Tonight I'll
make it come true ♪
[KANZAKI] Well, Toma Kamijo,
the rest is up to you.
[ARISA'S song] ♪ Your
smile is so dazzling ♪
♪ Let's make a chain spiraling ♪
♪ Through joining
hands we will be ♪
♪ A star in the whole sky ♪
♪ Tonight I'll make
it to come true ♪
♪ Oh please,
just let it come true ♪
♪ Our smiles are so dazzling
Links of our imagining ♪
♪ Create a future of light ♪
[CROWD cheering]
[beeping]
Where's our backup?
They say it'll
still be awhile.
Huh?
[MIKOTO grunts]
That dirty sneak!
Does he really think
he can leave me behind?
[MIKOTO] You'd think he would
know better than that by now.
Next time he won't forget!
Listen, you think
you can do me a favor?
Huh?
Stay here and keep
an eye on things.
You're going in
there without me?
You're the only person
I can ask. Please do it.
Hmm.
Good luck, Sissy!
[MIKOTO] I'm counting on you!
Be careful!
[whimpers]
♪
[STIYL] We're moving in.
--[MARYE] Right!
--[MARYBETH] Right, Master!
[JANE] Yes, sir!
Goodness. It looks like
quite a commotion down there.
It makes no difference;
they're all too late.
[SHUTAURA]
Are you sure about that?
[gun cocks]
♪
[LADYLEE] Silly girl. I
didn't think you would come.
[gunshot]
[LADYLEE retches]
I said I would stop you.
I intend to keep that promise.
[gunfire]
♪
[coughs]
[LADYLEE] I... I'm more than a
thousand years old, you know.
I was upset when the
Orion experiment failed.
But it was alright because
something unexpected
came out of it.
That something was Arisa.
[LADYLEE]
Her power is miraculous.
With it, I will be able to die.
What do you say?
Shall we end this together?
I don't think so!
[running footsteps]
♪
[grunting]
[SHUTAURA struggling]
[alarm beeping]
What's happening now?
[MIKOTO] Whoa! What that
was that? What happened?
Let's see. It isn't good.
It looks like there was
some kind of an explosion near
the elevator relay station.
[UIHARU] And, as a result,
the stress balances
are starting to come undone!
Wait, so,
are you saying?
[UIHARU]
If something isn't done,
the elevator is
going to collapse.
It will plummet
back down to Earth!
[CROWD commotion]
[MAN D] That sounded like
a freakin' huge explosion.
--[MAN E] No way.
--[WOMAN B] I'm scared!
[MAN G] Oh, man
we're in outer space!
[WOMAN C] What's
going to happen now?
[CROWD gasps and screams]
[WOMAN D]
Whoa, are you all right?
[MAN H] We're gonna die!
[CROWD commmotion]
[ARISA] Wait. What did
I do the last time?
Who's in charge?
Do something!
Get us out of
here already!
[ARISA] ♪ Wondering as I
look up to the stars above ♪
♪ If the sun will shine
tomorrow like it always does? ♪
♪ You and I go walking on,
under starlight so luminous ♪
--♪ "They look close ♪
--[FEMALE STUDENT A] A song?
--♪ enough to touch," ♪
♪ so we say ♪
♪ As we laugh
and stroll along ♪
♪
Okay, if you folks
will follow me, please?
♪ ...I thought of you ♪
♪ Reaching out to you ♪
♪ I text...
what I'm feeling ♪
♪ Anxiety buries me ♪
♪ Beneath my hopes... ♪
[LADYLEE] That's the...
thirty-eighth explosion...
I've been in...
It is the first time
I've ever been exposed
to a vacuum, though.
[LADYLEE]
This is it. I can tell.
Today is the day
I'm going to die!
What? Endymion is
going to collapse?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Yeah.
Apparently, that's unavoidable
at this point. We're doing
everything we can on our end,
but I just don't
think it's gonna--
[static interception]
Hey! Hello? You there?
What do we do?
[KAMIJO] We need to split up.
Huh?
It's the only way.
You keep the magic
from activating.
Meanwhile, I'll go after Arisa.
You're right.
We should split up.
But you had better save
her! You hear me, Toma?
She and I made a
promise to each other.
We promised once
her song was done
[INDEX] we would
sing it together.
I'll bring her back.
[ARISA'S song] ♪ If the
sun will shine tomorrow ♪
♪ like it always does? ♪
[UIHARU] It's no use!
There's nothing we can do
to prevent it from collapsing!
Just calm down and think.
[MIKOTO] There must be
something left to try.
Let me see.
[UIHARU] There is an
emergency purge system.
Under normal circumstances,
it would be set off remotely.
And with everything
that's going on right now,
the system
itself is frozen.
Is there a way to
get it working again?
[UIHARU] If we can manually
set off all the blast bolts
in these three spots,
then maybe.
It's a long shot,
but it could work.
[MIKOTO] Right now, we should
try anything we can.
I'll take one
of the locations.
I'll help you, Sissy. I'm
on my way there right now!
[groans]
But, you're in no shape!
I'll take the second location.
But we still
need someone else.
Alright, folks, we've only
got one more strike to go!
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Hello, ladies and gents!
Long time listener,
first time caller here!
It's a real pleasure
to be speaking with
all of you fine people!
I heard about your situation.
If you'll leave it
to me, I've got a way
[TSUCHIMIKADO] to deal
with the third blast bolt.
Who is that?
[ANTISKILL C] No idea.
I don't know who that is,
but if he can break in
on an Antiskill encrypted
line, chances are he's not
just some prankster.
We're out of time!
[MIKOTO] I say we let
the mystery man help.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] You get all that,
Stiyl? It's up to you, now.
Yeah, I got it.
I am at your service.
[SHUTAURA groans]
Make the noise stop!
Must make it stop!
Screeching like this
can work a miracle?
[SHUTAURA]
I will stop it. I swear!
[ARISA] ♪ If the sun will shine
tomorrow like it always does? ♪
♪ If you wish it hard enough ♪
♪ It's sure to
come true someday ♪
[ARISA] ♪ Just
believe in yourself ♪
--[SHUTAURA] No.
--♪ Wondering as I look up ♪
--[SHUTAURA] Stop it!
--♪ to the stars above ♪
[screams]
[KAMIJO panting]
[KAMIJO grunts]
[ARISA yelps]
[grunts]
Uh, where did
you come from?
Never mind that. I'm--
[grunts]
[gasps]
What's happening, Toma?
♪
Almost there.
A little farther.
[LADYLEE] It won't be long now.
[INDEX] I admit, I've never seen
a spell as crazy as this one.
Are you trying to
destroy the planet?
All the lines you've
used to refine your
magical power are skewed
way beyond what's rational.
You're the List
of Prohibited Books.
Yes, I've heard of you.
A human library.
[LADYLEE] A vessel for 103,000
volumes of magical grimoires.
I would think that
you would understand.
Surely you of all
people know what it's like
to be cursed by magic.
[LADYLEE] I want to
escape this living hell.
Please, won't you let me?
[INDEX] It won't work. Even
if this crazy plan succeeds,
you won't die. I can
tell you that much.
Uh!
Okay, here we go!
♪
Damn! If we don't hurry up,
it'll be too late
to do any good.
[MARYBETH] Uh!
[STIYL] Be more careful!
[MARYBETH] Sorry, Master!
Here they come!
[KAMIJO struggling]
What's the matter?
[footsteps]
[gun cocks]
[KAMIJO] Shutaura,
you don't need to do this!
[SHUTAURA]
This is all her fault.
Her existence is what
inspired Ladylee's plan...
and led to the unknown death.
Her stupid songs. The
supposed miracles they work
are nothing but illusions!
That's why she needs to die!
[SHUTAURA] How dare you?
This is no joke!
Ahhh!
[UIHARU] Okay, Misaka,
after your next right,
you should reach the target.
Got it, thanks!
[gasps]
[UIHARU] What is it, Misaka?
Is something wrong?
Are you okay?
Does it hurt badly?
Master.
Don't worry about me.
This is nothing but a scratch.
[MARYBETH and MARYE gasp]
Master. Allow us to
take care of this.
Now you're being ridiculous.
I told you, I'm fine.
I'm going to see this thing
through to the bitter end.
Yomikawa reporting in.
We're pinned down.
[YOMIKAWA] It doesn't look like
I'm going to get there in time.
[MISAKA 10032]
"That's acceptable."
[MISAKA 10032] "Please
proceed as planned and detonate
on the three-count as
previously determined,"
requests Misaka politely.
[KUROKO]
That sounded like Sissy.
[ACCELERATOR] Oh, come on.
Dragging me out of bed
for this? I was resting.
[ACCELERATOR] Why couldn't
they have left me in peace?
"Isn't it obvious?
If Endymion fell down,
[LAST ORDER] it would
mess up the whole planet,
and nobody would
have anywhere to live.
You wouldn't even have a
bed to get your rest in,"
says Misaka Misaka,
pointing out what must be
the most apparent reason.
Oh. Saving the Earth, huh?
Can't say I care about that,
but since I'm here anyway.
[ACCELERATOR] At least this'll
be good physical therapy.
[MIKOTO] There's no time for
hesitation now. Let's do this!
Three!
Two!
[yells]
What's happening now?
Did they do it?
Take cover!
[glass shattering]
[gasps]
[LADYLEE] What is this?
Are they activating the
elevator's purge system?
[INDEX] Okay, this is my chance.
I need to unpack the layers
of her spell. There must
be some way to collapse it.
They detonated
Endymion's base?
They're doing whatever
needs to be done.
Whatever it takes to
get everyone out of this.
[sighs]
[gun cocks]
[SHUTAURA] You don't get it.
My father was the
pilot of the Orion.
He was also the sole
casualty of that accident.
[SHUTAURA] I survived,
and so did the others.
All eighty-eight of us!
That's why I stopped believing
in so-called "miracles."
My father
didn't get a miracle.
[SHUTAURA] He fought
with everything he had
to save that plane. What
good did it do? He's dead!
It sounds like your
dad was a real hero.
He fought to protect you and
everyone else on the plane.
The odds were against him,
but he didn't let that
stop him from trying, right?
He did what he needed to do.
He stepped up to the plate.
He hung in there, believing
he could make a difference,
right 'til the very end.
And how did that turn out?
His daughter and everybody else
who was on the Orion survived.
[gasps]
[KAMIJO] Something
special happened.
There was a miracle that day.
And your father was part of it.
You do him a great
disservice by denying it.
It's like you're killing
him all over again.
Is that any way to honor
the memory of a true hero?
[gasps]
[cell phone vibrates]
Come on. Answer, already.
[SHUTAURA] Damn.
Endymion really
is going to fall.
You weren't bluffing.
[laughing]
To hell with the
Miracle of the Eighty-Eight,
you hear me? And to hell
with miraculous songs!
Go on. I'd like to see how
you're going to save us now!
You're going to
keep Endymion from
crashing down to
Earth, are you?
You're going to save
everybody from certain death?
[SHUTAURA] You'll
save her. And yourself.
And every other
idiot who prefers
to believe in miracles
instead of reality!
[gasps]
[beep]
[ARISA'S melody]
[groans]
No! Stop!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Denying that
miracles can happen
doesn't help anything!
Belief is what saves people!
[grunts]
[KAMIJO] Ah!
[grunting]
[ARISA'S melody continues]
To get what you want in
life, you have to believe
you can do the impossible.
You have to pick a
dream and strive for it,
no matter what happens.
That's the only way you can
hope to make a difference.
To change the
world for the better!
[KAMIJO] Think about it!
That's what your father did
on the plane that day.
His belief that he
could do the impossible
was the true miracle!
[grunts]
You've got it wrong.
You're the one who
won't face reality.
So I'm going to
destroy your illusion!
[grunts]
[pained yell]
[SHUTAURA grunts]
[shaky exhale]
[KAMIJO] Hey,
you know, Shutaura,
music can be beautiful.
It really can.
[thud]
[KAMIJO] Damn it.
[KAMIJO] Not yet.
It's not over yet.
[SHUTAURA singing
ARISA'S melody]
[KAMIJO exhales heavily]
[SHUTAURA singing
ARISA'A melody]
[singing continues]
[worried chatter]
[beeping]
[COPILOT] The left engine
block has fallen away!
We won't make it. It's over!
Don't you dare give up now.
There must be
something that we can do!
[COPILOT panicking]
[PILOT] Stay calm.
[COPILOT screams]
[PILOT] Hey!
[YOUNG SHUTAURA]
Please, I'm begging you.
I'll sacrifice everything
that's precious to me.
Just please.
Work a miracle for us!
[grunts]
[SHUTAURA] That's right.
[SHUTAURA] Before we crashed,
I made a desperate wish.
I asked for a
miracle to happen.
I offered a sacrifice.
And then...
[ARISA] And then I was born.
[ARISA singing melody]
[ARISA] ♪ A symphony... ♪
What is that? A song?
[LADYLEE]
Oh no! It has to stop!
It's going to ruin everything!
Please stop this!
If that song keeps going,
if that kind of
power is released,
it'll fall apart.
My dream will be over!
[LADYLEE]
Please, this isn't fair!
[ARISA and SHUTAURA] ♪ And now
I know that I can sing ♪
♪ I have the
power to illuminate ♪
♪ Allowing love to
find a way, back to us ♪
♪ Here in eternity
may it rest ♪
♪ And then I know
I'll sing to you ♪
[ARISA and SHUTAURA] ♪ There's
nothing more that I could ♪
♪ lose from this ♪
What's happening, sir?
What do we do now?
It's gonna fall down!
[STIYL grunts]
[JANE, MALYBETH,
and MARYE scream]
"Wow! We're flying
through the air!"
exclaims Misaka Misaka.
[ACCELERATOR] Tch.
This is a one-time thing.
You understand that, right?
[MIKOTO panting]
[ARISA and SHUTAURA]
♪ And over again ♪
♪ Into the skies... ♪
The captain's up there.
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, look.
There's been a change.
Endymion is moving away from
[UIHARU] its previous
course of descent.
It's going to avoid a
collision with the Earth!
[ARISA and SHUTAURA]
♪ ...my wings ♪
[shaky breathing]
You did it after all.
[KAMIJO] I'm sure the
entire world heard it.
It was a beautiful song.
Hmmm.
[shaky exhales]
[thud]
[birds chirping]
[LAURA] I can't help but wonder.
What exactly do you suppose
that young woman was?
Quite a unique situation.
[ALEISTER] It certainly was.
If I had to guess,
I would say that
the girl was a wish.
A wish?
[ALEISTER] A person's wish
can distort their subjectivity.
This holds true even
if the person is not,
in fact, an esper.
And if multiple people
were to make the same wish
at the same exact time,
that wish might even have
the power to interfere
with causality.
Put it out, Master.
[ALEISTER] It might
divide a young girl into
two different
selves and thus alter
the fate of a
great many people.
Yes, I see now. There
would be more distortion to
the fabric of reality when
the two became one again,
which would result
in the occurrence of
yet another miracle.
[ALEISTER] Ladylee has
performed quite a fascinating
experiment for me.
The poor thing.
How unfortunate for
her that she cannot die.
[INDEX] So, what do you think?
Was Arisa a real person?
I think so.
She must have been.
I touched her
with my right hand.
So she wasn't an illusion,
or she would have disappeared.
[KAMIJO] I think she was real.
Someone who liked music.
And to sing her own songs.
A normal girl who liked
to make others happy.
Yeah. I think so, too.
Uh.
Huh?
[BOTH shaky exhales]
[BOTH gasp excitedly]
Mmm, ha!
[INDEX] Toma, did you
hear what I just heard?
[KAMIJO] Yeah!
♪