[GARAK]
Ryu.
Ryu!
[GARAK]
Are you done checking?
Very interesting.
Yatsufusa, look at this.
[YATSUFUSA]
I like it.
Should be very challenging.
I'm happy we asked for
Ryu's opinion, then.
[bell ringing]
[SERVANT A]
Excuse me.
Put this into effect.
[SERVANT A]
Certainly, ma'am.
[MITSUHIDE]
This is the examination period
for applicants to become
apprentice court herbalists.
[ZEN]
I see. So it was today.
What do you mean, "I see"?
Let's not pretend you
haven't been worried
about this test for weeks.
[SHIRAYUKI] As I continue this
path, I know nothing is certain.
How will it look,
sound, or even smell?
The only thing I do know?
I'll learn something
new every day.
[SERVANT B] Once all the
examinees have arrived,
we will proceed to
the orientation room.
Please wait
patiently until then.
I'm nervous.
Don't worry it won't
be much longer.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI] I think that might
be the same court herbalist
I saw at the pharmacy
the other day.
A compound for
suppressing coughs?
That's a good start,
but he'd still need some
rainbow leaf and koko grass.
Sorry, sir! Forgive me.
Yes, I will need some
rainbow leaf and koko grass,
but they're not
ready to pick yet.
I'll do it right at dawn,
when the medicinal properties
are at their most effective.
When they're at
their most effective?
That's right, I've heard
of that technique before!
And you know when?
[RYU] Yes, it took
centuries to figure this out
by the ancient folk who lived
in nature and off the land.
Current medical literature
has no category for it,
but I remembered
because it's important.
The people who spent time
studying the actual plants
knew best.
I'd much rather learn
my skills from them.
I hope I get the chance to learn
about living medicine here.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen!
Your test starts soon.
Think you're ready for it?
Kind of.
What do you mean, "kind of"?
Wish me luck!
I am the chief herbalist,
Garak. Welcome.
This exam will
measure your ability
to manage both herb gardens
and medicine storage,
as that's the primary work of
a court herbalist apprentice.
You will be responsible for
a small medicinal herb garden
in the castle,
protecting and tending
to the environment
and plants inside the garden.
After two days, there
will be an inspection,
and following, you
will submit a report.
That is all. Please read the
documents for further details.
[OBI] Well, isn't she
just a model student.
[ZEN]
How did it get so late?
[SHIRAYUKI] They're using
aqueducts to make sure
the entire
garden is irrigated.
I've heard of these,
but I've never actually
seen them until now.
Such an efficient system!
Oh, no, some mud
got into the water.
[ZEN]
I thought I saw some lights on.
It's not even dawn yet.
What is she doing?
[rustling]
[ZEN]
Who's there?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
Hey, Shirayuki!
You startled me.
What're you doing here?
Wait! Stay where you are--
[BOTH gasp]
[ZEN]
Great, we're locked in.
[SHIRAYUKI]
We are?
[ZEN]
Do you know who might do this?
Was someone meeting you here?
[SHIRAYUKI]
What?
No, I'm in the middle of my
apprentice exam right now.
[ZEN]
Interesting.
They must've locked
us in knowing that.
Let's just wait.
Whoever comes to conduct
the inspection in the morning
can let us out.
[ZEN] Yes, but my being
here would be problematic
if they think I'm helping you.
Hey, speaking of.
Was there a particular
reason you came by?
Uh, no, I was just...
in the neighborhood.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, I see.
[sighs]
I feel like an idiot, now.
When did you first
get here again?
Yesterday.
[ZEN]
Did you get enough sleep?
I took a little nap.
Sometimes, it seems like you're
sidestepping the real question.
Well, how could
I think of sleep
when I had the opportunity
to be inside such a rare
and beautiful garden?
Something wrong?
This flower.
It should be blooming
facing upward
from late at night
until morning, so why...?
[SHIRAYUKI] There's water
flowing underneath it.
There are no irregularities
in its environment,
yet the flowers are wilting.
The water is sweet?
[SHIRAYUKI]
But up here, it's normal.
So, what's the verdict?
There're some
toxins in this water.
Toxins?
And you decided to drink it?!
Uh... Don't worry.
It doesn't affect humans.
Are you... Are you sure?
[ZEN]
Don't scare me like that.
I'm sorry.
Well? Explain it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, right.
Of the toxins that medicinal
herbs and plants can carry,
one of them tastes
a lot like honey.
I think someone mixed it
in with the water.
I don't see the plant that
makes that toxin, though.
[SHIRAYUKI] The water up top is
clean, so it must be down here.
What herb would've
made that toxin?
Hold on.
This may be yura shigure,
and not akegi shigure.
[ZEN]
Huh?
[SHIRAYUKI]
If the roots are sweet...
It's yura!
You're certain?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes.
There are two types,
yura and akegi,
and it's hard to tell the
difference until they flower.
This yura plant was grown in
the same environment to bloom
as an akegi would be.
So are you saying it
was actually planted
in the wrong way?
If in a foreign environment,
yura will be unable to bloom,
and their roots
will produce toxins,
which would flow into the
aqueducts from the soil.
[SHIRAYUKI]
If this keeps up,
the yura and the other
plants will wither and die.
Zen!
Close the aqueduct from
here to the other side!
I can dig these out
and replant them all.
That's all right?
If I help you,
it might negatively
affect your test score.
True, but I have to do
what's necessary to fix this.
Are you sure you won't
get disqualified or fail?
[SHIRAYUKI] As long as
he's a part of my path,
I don't think I'll ever fail.
If I stay on track,
I'll be fine.
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're my guide.
I have the strength
to do anything, now.
And that's all because
of your help, Zen.
Well, then. How could I resist?
I'll help you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Rainbow leaf and koko grass.
[door opens]
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's the Chief! Good morning!
Good morning.
Why are you in the
garden, Your Highness?
I'll explain it later.
[GARAK] Shirayuki,
what happened in here?
I rearranged things so the
yura shigure would flower.
It had been mistakenly
planted as akegi shigure.
[GARAK]
You figured that out?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes.
[GARAK] And replanted
the rest of the garden?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes.
I wanted to make sure
they wouldn't be affected
by the remaining toxins
in the aqueducts.
You did this in one night?
Did you receive any
help from the prince?
Well, I thought it made sense.
After all, some of these herbs
just might save
his life one day.
[ZEN chuckles]
I suppose that's a
logical explanation.
There was an examinee
who was mistaken
for a prowler last night.
That person must've
locked the door.
Perhaps a competitor wants
to eliminate Shirayuki.
Perhaps.
I can assure you, this matter
will be investigated thoroughly.
I can tell you the person
was wearing a long coat,
and had tied-back hair all
the way down to the waist.
[GARAK]
Thank you, Highness.
Shirayuki, please know
there's a proper time and place
for your friendship
with the prince.
Yes. I understand, ma'am.
Hold on, it was my
choice to come here.
Prince Zen, your status
affords you carte blanche
to make all decisions
without being challenged.
All it takes is
one word from you.
Your friend could be accepted
as a court herbalist
unconditionally,
with no further questions asked.
She's too proud for that.
Plus, if I did, she'd get mad at
me and leave the castle grounds.
And the last thing I want
to do is make her angry.
I'll take that as a compliment.
[GARAK laughing]
[YATSUFUSA]
Chief!
[GARAK]
Sorry.
How did Shirayuki fare
on the test, Yatsufusa?
[GARAK laughing]
She has passed
with flying colors.
Well then, congratulations.
Shirayuki, you have
officially been accepted
as an apprentice
court herbalist.
[GARAK chuckles]
[GARAK] The examination
was not just about
testing your knowledge
of tending gardens,
but about yura and akegi, too,
and if you knew the difference.
It would have been enough
if you had just noticed
and wrote it in the records.
But I didn't think anyone
would actually replant
the whole garden.
[GARAK chuckles]
Ryu's going to be in
for a real surprise.
Ryu?
[GARAK] That's right. Our
youngest court herbalist.
He's the one who
devised today's exam.
The quiet one? With black hair?
Indeed. It seems
you've already met.
All right.
Then we'll appoint him
to be your supervisor.
Great!
Oh!
Chief Garak, please.
I'd like to ask your
permission for something.
[GARAK] The two of you are
the only ones this time
who have passed the exam
to become court
herbalist apprentices.
Higata, please wait a moment.
I'm coming in!
This is Shirayuki, she's going
to be your new assistant.
She did an outstanding
job on your test.
I'm Ryu. Hello.
If there's anything you have
questions about, just ask him.
Come on, let's get back to work.
Hi, I'm Shirayuki.
It's lovely to meet you.
[RYU] Same here.
Could you close the door?
Oh, right! Sorry about that.
Um, Ryu, sir?
[RYU]
Please don't call me "sir."
In fact, you don't have
to be formal at all.
What? Pardon?
I mean-- But you're
going to be my superior.
I know, but I'm only
a kid. It's just weird.
Okay, I'll use your first name,
if you prefer that, Ryu.
Oh, hey!
Here. A gift.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Rainbow leaf and koko grass.
Picked at sunrise,
when their medicinal properties
are strongest, like you said.
You remembered that?
[SHIRAYUKI] Yes, because
I was a little shocked by it.
How do you mean?
I thought it was an innovative
and wonderful idea.
I'll grind the herbs up.
You put in the rainbow leaf
first, and koko grass second.
Sure.
[bell ringing]
[SHIRAYUKI]
How can we help you today, sir?
For some reason, I've
been feeling queasy.
I'm wondering if you have
a quick remedy for nausea.
[SHIRAYUKI] Certainly.
Ryu, please come in here.
What?!
I can't do anything for him.
He should go see the
chief, or someone else.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ryu?
I'm so glad he left.
I want no part of any
concoction that boy's prepared.
Why would you say
something like that?
Who'd want his help?
His principal studies
are plant poisons.
And he needs a way to
test out their effects.
The only way he could do that
is to try them on humans.
Some plants must create toxins
to help protect themselves
from predators.
And these same toxins are often
used to cure sick people!
Yes, but according
to the rumors,
there's a trail of victims--
If you believe
everything you hear,
you'll never trust
anyone or anything!
Now do you want help,
or don't you?
Uh, yeah.
Please excuse me.
[RYU] There's no need to
get so worked up about it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Well, you're being stupid.
I'll go get the chief herbalist.
What? Stupid?
[ZEN] So how's it
going with Shirayuki?
[RYU]
Your Highness.
She was angry at me.
I-- I guess I don't really
understand people very well.
But it's not like they
understand me, either.
Seems like most think
I'm just a dumb brat.
[ZEN] The answer to this
is really quite simple.
If you want to know if
she's mad, just ask her.
She'll appreciate the gesture.
She's a very
straightforward person herself.
For the record, I know
you're not dumb.
I just thought you might
like a little advice.
--[bell tolls]
--Uh?
I gotta go to practice. See ya.
[GARAK]
Shirayuki,
once you finish the patient
records, please read this.
It's the prince's
medical history.
I thought you might
wanna look it over.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thanks, but why me?
Because out of all
the court herbalists,
you seem to have the closest
relationship with him.
It may help you deal
with emergencies,
not to mention
helping your resolve.
[SHIRAYUKI] Here's all the
medication for past injuries.
A scratch and a sprain from
a rough sword practice.
A bruise from falling
off the castle wall.
Why was he even up there?
Zen, at age 13.
Poisoning symptoms
and progression?
[SHIRAYUKI]
A record of being poisoned?
February fifth.
Seven hours after
administration,
he broke out in a high fever.
[GARAK] Breathing was shallow.
Speech and conduct were normal.
Remained stable for 31 hours.
May the 11th.
Right after administration,
he had difficulty walking.
Called for antidote
three hours later.
July the first.
Thirty minutes post
administration,
he began to run a fever.
[SHIRAYUKI] With stabbing
pains all over his body.
I've been building up
an immunity to poisons.
[SHIRAYUKI cyring]
[RYU]
Prince Zen!
Ryu! What's wrong?
Uh, I, um.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, but-- I just--
I thought that I should
come and get you.
Your friend may be in trouble.
She's crying! By herself.
I don't know why.
[ZEN]
You read the history.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes. How did you know?
[ZEN]
It's about me. And I know you.
Please, just turn around.
I'll stay until you're done.
Okay, Shirayuki? Don't cry.
[SHIRAYUKI]
All right.
[KIKI]
Are you still thirsty?
[MITSUHIDE]
How about some snacks?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ryu!
Hey!
Are you all right?
Zen just talked to me.
It seems like I might've scared
you a little bit. I'm sorry.
No, it's my fault.
I really didn't mean
to make you cry.
I'm sorry that I was
being stupid.
It's okay.
Remember my name?
It's long, I know.
Uh. Yeah, I guess so.
Very well, if you
call me by my name,
I'll tell you if I'm mad or not.
Uh.
No, I uh...
She'll appreciate the gesture.
She's a very
straightforward person herself.
[RYU]
Sh--
Sh-- Shira--
Shira...yuki.
[SHIRAYUKI chuckles]
Right!
[gasps]
Ryu, thanks for
running here for me.
Uh, yeah.
[SHIRAYUKI laughing]
Yura shigure.
Isn't that the flower that
was on the herbalist exam?
Is yura shigure your favorite
of the medicinal herbs, Ryu?
[RYU]
Uh-huh.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Is there a reason?
[RYU]
Because it's red and pretty.
[ZEN]
I'd like to see it again.
Apparently, it's important to
become more familiar with it.
Is he jealous?
Green-eyed monster.
I don't mind taking
you to see it again.
I learn something
new every day.
People aren't that
different from flowers.
In order to know about them,
you have to embrace
the bitter and the sweet,
both in them, and yourself.
That's how we know
who we really are.
And that's how we grow.
[OBI] What if the illness really
is the work of some evil spirit?
[MITSUHIDE] As a prince,
it's your duty to stay healthy.
[ZEN]
I can't leave you alone
after bringing you
into this mess.
[OBI]
Why do I wanna follow her?