[SHIRAYUKI grunts, sighs]
[ZEN]
Shirayuki,
my title might not always
be able to protect you.
I don't care that it may
not be easy, though.
Together, we can
weather the storms.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Later on, when Zen was leaving,
he said, "see ya later,"
like he usually does.
And I knew, everything
would be all right.
[CROWD chattering]
Oh, so many people!
They look like
they're having fun.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Open Castle Day? What's that?
Once every few years,
part of the castle is
open to the public,
and they make it
a festive event.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Wow!
[RYU] They have all kinds of
activities for people, too.
[GARAK] Even so, it's business
as usual for us herbalists.
After you've reached
a good stopping point,
feel free to go look.
Oh, Thanks!
This seems like something
Zen would love.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[ZEN] Shirayuki, that area's
open to the public,
so it's very crowded.
This way.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[SHILA]
Uh. Hi, Shirayuki.
[KAI gasps]
Prince Zen?!
[BOTH gasp]
[ZEN] Today'll be busy, but I
know you both can handle it!
Sir!
You can count on us!
Aw, C'mon! That's not fair.
You just stole my line!
[SHIRAYUKI panting]
[ZEN] Could you tell that
it was me behind you?
Well, your voice gave you away,
but why are you dressed
up as a guard?
I wasn't needed right away,
so I decided to go undercover.
I wanted to check on castle
staff, and see the citizens.
This lets me do both
at the same time.
That's very Zen of you,
but don't make anyone mad.
Not to mention that...
I wanted to spend time with you.
Just us two.
Just us?
[gasps]
[thump]
What's that?
Uh... Uh! That's, uh.
That's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
Great, you found me.
Thanks, you guys.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh!
Are we interrupting
something? So sorry.
Hey there, Shirayuki.
Zen, you can't wander off.
A reminder:
Even though the public areas of
the castle are limited today,
you still need to be careful
about where you go.
Well, excuse me for
wanting to stroll solo.
Mitsuhide was getting
pretty worried about you.
Obi, we agreed to keep
that between us.
Kiki, do I still have some time?
[KIKI]
Yes, but not much.
Excellent. What about you?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh? Mm-hm.
All right, it's settled then!
The five of us are going to take
a small trip around the grounds.
Welcome, friends, come on over!
We have all kinds of goodies!
Wow, there are food stalls, too?
[ZEN] We brought them in from
the castle town just for today.
Nice, they've got liquor, too.
Now's not the time for drinking.
[BOY 12A]
Hurry, mama!
[MITSUHIDE]
Whoops.
Watch where you're
goin', little man!
[KIKI]
It's really getting busy now.
[MITSUHIDE]
Well, it is almost lunchtime.
Hang on. This isn't
normal, is it?
Have you worn that hood before?
[SHIRAYUKI] Mm-hm. Though,
I don't wear it a lot,
I just like to avoid attention
when I'm in a big
crowd like this.
[OBI] Mm. Gotcha. I guess your
hair does kinda stand out.
Huh.
Looks like some entertainment
might be about to start.
I wonder what it is.
Let's go check it out.
[OBI] Has Shirayuki had
problems with her hair
getting the
wrong attention?
Ah.
Then, I don't blame her
for keeping that bright
color under wraps.
Neither do I.
People can be morons.
But it sure is pretty.
[CROWD cheers]
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Hm?
The other day, Zen
told us something.
Kiki, Obi, Mitsuhide.
From now on, I have
chosen one path.
The one that allows me
to be with Shirayuki.
And I've told her
that's what I want.
So, what did she say?
She said she'd take my hand.
[MITSUHIDE]
That's so great!
Ah. Well done.
He said he wants
to be with you.
And that he'd do whatever
it took to make it happen.
Is that what you want,
as well, Shirayuki?
It absolutely is.
That's really great news.
Because we want
that for you, too.
Thanks!
[SHIRAYUKI laughs]
Where did Obi go?
I don't know
[SPECTATORS cheer]
[FIGHTER A grunts]
[REFEREE A] End match!
The winner is... Nanaki!
[CROWD cheers]
[OBI] Hey, Master! Did you
watch me win that match?
Look, I got a prize!
You're not supposed to
disappear like that!
And who's this 'Nanaki', anyway?
For tournaments like this,
I use a stage name so
I can feel famous.
You're a very strange man.
Couldn't care less
about the stage name.
What I wanna know is
how you acquired
those amazing combat
skills, Obi!
[OBI] Wanna fight me sometime
and find out, Mitsuhide?
Yeah, you're on!
Zen, it's about
time to get going.
Right. I'll see you later.
[ZEN]
Obi, take good care of her.
He's gotta greet the
crowd with Izana.
Wanna go watch 'em?
Of course.
[OBI]
Before we do, though.
[gasps]
[OBI]
I want you to have this.
I won it in the fight.
It's an imported hair ornament.
Make sure you show
the master later.
[bell tolls]
[CROWD cheering]
[FEMALE A]
Prince Izana! Prince Zen!
You are the best princes
in the entire world,
and we love you so much!
[MALE B] Prince Zen has become
a very dignified young man!
[OBI] Ah... It's like he's
a whole a different person.
[IZANA] Zen, have you changed
your mind since we spoke?
About what?
[IZANA] I was wondering if you
have plans regarding the girl.
[ZEN] Lord Brother, you think
now's the time for this?
[IZANA]
Why not?
[ZEN] I've been thinking about
it a great deal, in fact.
About our future.
[SHIRAYUKI] Sometimes, when I
see Zen around the castle,
we get to have little moments
together like earlier.
And then when we part.
I still feel like he's
right there with me.
But the truth is,
in this castle, I'll always
be far away from him.
Even so, he's worth it.
[MITSUHIDE] Nicely done.
What's on the agenda now?
Oh, don't know yet.
Uh!
[ZEN]
Ryu!
[RYU]
Uh?
Where's Shirayuki?
I can't find her!
[ZEN]
Is there something wrong?
Yeah, a performer got hurt!
[ZEN gasps]
Look you, sir.
Are you trying to test me?
That would be unwise.
No, of course I'm
not, your highness!
[PRINCE] Then, why would
you say such a thing?
This is a place of celebration.
It is highly inappropriate.
[KNIGHT] I just wanted to
get to know you better...
[ACTRESS groans]
[ACTRESS]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
She tripped while
she was on stage.
[ACTRESS groans]
I need something.
Anything to take this pain away!
Please, I still have
to go back on stage!
What?
You heard me!
It hurts so bad.
Because it's broken.
You need to stay off it
so it can heal. Sorry.
Oh, no.
[TROUPE LEADER]
Aw!
This was my chance to shine,
so I'd be invited to the castle.
Now, the princes are never
going to fall in love with me!
Now's your chance.
[ZEN grunts]
You're just looking for a reward
so you can make yourself
some pretty new costumes!
Don't be stupid! I'm an
actress, so of course!
I want to stand
on a grand stage,
wear beautiful clothes,
and be famous.
Uh?
Just kill me.
This is so embarrassing.
Don't worry. I think
you're wonderful, ma'am.
Uh... Uh!
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Right.
[BOTH gasp]
It's beautiful!
First, we have to
stabilize the injury.
'Scuse me. Would you mind
standing in for her?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Hm?
[ZEN]
Uh!
[TROUPE LEADER]
Please, miss.
Please go on stage
as the princess!
Ah...
What?!
I must determine whether
the prince is truly suitable
for my sweet princess.
A test, if you will.
However, the prince is always
careful, and he is never alone.
Are you ready to go on?
[KNIGHT]
I must hurry.
It will be too late after
something has happened.
Too late!
Well, here goes nothing.
[ZEN]
Uh.... Right, sure.
[OBI] You look a little
red there, master.
[ZEN]
No, I don't. Shut up.
[ACTRESS A] The actor on stage
right now is playing the knight
who serves the princess.
The eve before the wedding,
he will test the prince's
worthiness of her.
And they will have a duel to
see which one is stronger.
The princess will
make her appearance
before any of that happens, but
she only has one line to say.
You can just follow my
lead for where to stand.
Right. I think I can do it.
I need to keep my hair
covered up, though.
Good point. Best not
to startle anyone.
I'm afraid I disagree.
I think they should be
startled, in a good way.
[KNIGHT]
I swear!
Tonight, on this very sword!
On my very body, I swear!
Ready? You're
almost up, princess.
The time has come to find out
what this prince is made of!
[AUDIENCE applauds]
[sighs] You the one standing in?
Yes, and I'll try
not to mess it up!
[PRINCE] What?! We can't just
alter the entire scene!
Don't question me
now, just do it!
I promise you, this will
finally take the troupe
from being third-rate hacks
to celebrated stars overnight!
Don't let me down!
Oh, fine, whatever.
You're on. You'll do great!
Oh, yeah, thanks.
The actress was injured. I just
hope it wasn't too severe.
As do I. Mm?
Something wrong?
Kiki, I think that's...
It's Shirayuki?
Princess! Please, you
must listen to me!
Uh. Yes. Yes!
Good girl, she said it.
Twice, in fact, you think she
might be a little nervous?
It doesn't matter, now.
All she has left to do is be
kissed on the back of her hand.
Ya look a little
red there, master.
[ZEN]
I can't allow it.
[OBI]
Huh?
I mean, I won't allow it.
Shirayuki is not an actress.
This farce needs
to end right now.
Where has the
troupe leader gone?
[TROUPE LEADER chuckles]
Wait, what's going on here?
The prince is saying
totally different lines.
Princess, may I ask you to
kindly pray upon my sword?
My princess.
Come on. Just say it.
Hurry up, man.
[OBI] What are you doin'
behind this curtain,
Mister Troupe Leader?
[OBI] He wants to expose
Shirayuki's hair?
What would he do that for?!
Hair like hers appears
maybe once in a lifetime!
How could I not show it off?
[OBI]
Seriously?
It's too late to stop the play.
Besides, this'll finally give my
troupe the success we deserve!
Because the brightest star
of this entire performance
will be that
spectacular red hair!
Okay, wait for it. This is
the high point of the show!
Ah, princess. You
are at last my wife.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Get in there and stop it!
[ZEN]
Sir Knight. A moment, please?
[KNIGHT gasps]
What the... What do
you think you're doing?!
[OBI] The master doesn't care
for your idea too much.
[gasps]
He's probably gonna rewrite
your play a little bit more.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ah!
Fair princess, stay back.
The sword that doth protect
you, belongs to me!
[PRINCE]
Uh...
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ah...
En garde. Draw your
sword, Highness!
[PRINCE whimpers]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[ACTRESS A]
I'm so sorry, Miss!
I swear I had no idea they
were planning to do that!
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's all right.
Good work out there.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Why did Zen go on stage?
Ah.
Well, it is the
real prince's duty
to protect his princess, right?
[OBI] Your hair. The kiss on
your hand from someone else.
Our sweet prince was jealous.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?
Poor master. That look on his
face gave everything away.
I can read that
guy like a book.
He's a page turner.
[SHIRAYUKI] Zen has always
been honest with me.
About his feelings, and
especially his passion.
[SHIRAYUKI] I'll always know
how important they are.
After all, he inspires
them in me, too.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's so funny.
I never imagined we'd wind
up on a stage together!
[ZEN]
Seriously.
I'd like to watch the same play
as part of the
audience next time.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Me, too.
[ZEN] It felt strange to play a
knight dueling with a prince.
I really enjoyed it, though.
I even got to keep this mask.
If I may, Sir Knight,
you wear it well.
Uh. What is that?
Oh, Obi gave it to me earlier.
It's the prize he got
for winning the match.
[ZEN]
That scoundrel.
It's like he's trying
to irritate me...
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?
But I admit, it looks good.
Uh. Mm... Thank you.
I guess I won't
take it off, then.
[ZEN] Did you have to
keep your hair covered
when you were living
in Tanbarun?
[SHIRAYUKI] No, it was
always out in the open.
Even after I first moved to
Clarines, I let everyone see it.
[ZEN] That's true.
I saw it when we met.
If it's okay to ask you, there's
something I've been wondering.
Has it... ever caused
you problems?
Other than Raj, I mean.
At times, for sure.
But I figured out
how to deal with it.
My grandparents helped me
get through it all, too.
[ZEN]
Your grandparents?
Yes.
I learned so much about
how to live your life
from the two of them. They
were always planning ahead
to when I'd eventually
have to fend for myself.
They told me there'd be
times when it seemed
like I couldn't count on
anyone else in this world.
That's when I'd have
to take care of myself
and be my own strongest ally.
And... they were so right.
I understand.
Since the day I met
you, I noticed that.
How independent you are,
and how you don't like
asking people for help.
I guess they were the ones
who instilled that in you.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Though, as of late, I--
No. I rely on you, too.
[ZEN]
Uh?
I know I may not always show it,
but at this moment, I do.
I have for a while, now.
I think you bring out
the best in me!
[ZEN]
Really?
[SHIRAYUKI] Mm-hm. I'm glad I
trusted myself and stayed here.
Zen. Will give me
your hand, again?
[ZEN]
Mm?! Sure.
This is exactly where
I want to be. With you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Um. Uh!
I'm not very good
at stuff like this.
Sorry if it got weird.
No, it's fine!
Yeah.
[CROWD cheers]
[SHIRAYUKI, ZEN]
Uh?
[SHIRAYUKI]
What are those?
[ZEN]
It's how this day ends.
The Open Castle finale.
We wish on the lights, and
release them into the sky.
Would you like to go
take a closer look?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm-hm!
[ZEN]
Oh, Shirayuki!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[ZEN]
Just until we get outside.
[MITSUHIDE growls]
Zen.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
I'm right here, calm yourself.
[MITSUHIDE]
Too late!
Did I or did I not warn
you to be careful
what you did in public?!
Apparently, Mitsuhide
saw the play.
Oh, I see.
[CROWD cheers]
Wow, so pretty!
[ZEN grunts]
Oh, shut up.
It's really kinda sweet.
You fuss over the Master
almost like you're
his father, Mitsuhide.
It's my job, and I'm
rather fond of him.
Remember that time
you two argued
and he wouldn't talk
to you for a while.
So you went on
that hunger strike
until he spoke to you again?
Come on, it was
only for one day!
It would've been two, but I
couldn't last any longer.
Two days?
Impressive, who knew
you were that immature?
[ZEN]
Ok, That's enough, you guys.
Listen. Shirayuki
already knows this,
but whatever the
future may hold.
I can't envision it without
each and every one of you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen, look, it's beautiful!
Is it just me, or has somethin'
changed with him recently?
He's just asserting himself.
[MITSUHIDE] You might have
to work harder. For once.
[SHIRAYUKI] We all chose
to travel the same path.
And while this moment
is truly wonderful,
there might be difficult
times ahead.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'm not too worried, though.
Because I know there
will be happiness.
[SHIRAYUKI] As long as
we continue forward,
joy is guaranteed.
[SHIRAYUKI]
We'll walk this path together.