[SHIRAYUKI]
Found it!
The spellami herb. It's
an ao shidare perennial.
If you steam and dry the
roots, it can lower fevers,
and alleviate pain, too.
[bell tolling]
Oh, my goodness.
Gotta open the shop!
[SHIRAYUKI]
This is it. My own path.
It's my story.
[SHIRAYUKI]
If I had my way,
I would keep charting
my own path like this.
No rules.
[chuckling]
[RAJ]
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest of them all?
Tell me true.
Your Highness.
What now, Sakaki?
[SAKAKI] This is in fact
an informant from town.
I'm afraid he is not a mirror.
[RAJ]
Ahem.
He's telling me what he sees,
that's basically the same thing.
[SAKAKI sighs]
Still, please try to take
things more seriously.
Informant!
Don't just sit there.
Start talking!
[INFORMANT]
Uh, yes, Highness!
You wanna know who
the most beautiful girl
in the kingdom of
Tanbarun is, right?
Well, there is...
this girl I know of.
And who is this girl?
[INFORMANT]
Ah,
she is a maiden born with
exceptionally rare red hair,
as bright and rosy
as a ripe apple.
Her name is Shirayuki, Highness.
[CHILD]
Thank you, miss! Bye, bye!
Goodbye. Take your medicine now!
[YOSHI]
See ya soon, Miss Shirayuki.
Okay. Feel better, Yoshi.
Thanks for your patience.
You're still waiting for
your medicine, right, Kino?
Yes, but please,
take your time,
I just came to let my eyes
rest on your beautiful hair.
I've never seen anything
quite so extraordinary!
That's so sweet. Thank you.
But since I already
have you here,
I'll start preparing
another remedy.
I found some good
medicinal herbs,
so please take some with you.
[KINO crying]
You have turned into a
very fine young herbalist.
If only your late grandparents
could see this.
They would be
beaming with pride.
Oh, no. Kino, please don't--
Oh, my goodness! I believe I
left the stove on, I must go!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
[KINO]
Oh dear, silly me.
[KINO chuckling]
I guess I can just
take it to her later.
Did you forget something?
You said Prince
Raj's... concubine?
Yes. In other words,
you would be his mistress.
Absurd!
I can't believe
he'd be interested
in a common girl like me
just because of the
color of my hair.
I'd be an embarrassment to him.
Still, Prince Raj has
taken a liking to you.
Therefore, you are required
to formally appear
at the castle tomorrow morning.
I suggest you look presentable.
[SHIRAYUKI] For Kino,
something to ease her back pain
and her inflamed
respiratory tract.
At Yuri's place, both
the father and the baby
were starting to come
down with colds.
Yes, so who's next?
That takes care of everyone.
[SHIRAYUKI] Please know
this wasn't your fault.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Goodbye, Tanbarun.
I'll miss you.
[knocking]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Excuse me!
Is anyone home?
May I come inside?
[SHIRAYUKI sighs]
[SHIRAYUKI] I can't just
go in without being invited.
But it's already getting dark.
[SHIRAYUKI]
And I'm starting to get hungry.
[MAN] Mitsuhide, Kiki!
I'm going on ahead!
[MITSUHIDE] Hey, careful,
braggart! You'll hurt yourself.
[gasps]
[thud]
I told you so, Zen!
Are you hurt? Did you
fall on your head?
Tell me, what's one plus one?
Purple.
Wait. Who're you again?
It's me, Mitsuhide!
Oh, I forgot.
Was that your name?
Kiki! Not helping
even a little bit!
[ZEN laughing]
[ZEN]
Hold.
Mind telling me who you are?
And what you're doing
in the woods all alone.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, I just, uh...
I just left my home,
and I was in a hurry
so I got rather lost and ended
up on a random road and...
...I'm here.
You have very unusual hair.
Yeah, I know.
I hear that frequently.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, your arm. It's injured!
Eh, I've had worse.
You're in luck.
I'm an herbalist.
I have a healing poultice
you can use on it, that'll help.
[ZEN]
No, thanks.
It could be poison or something.
I'm not going to fall
for that little trick.
I wasn't born yesterday, y'know.
Trust is something
earned, not given.
In other words, we're done here.
Oh.
So, off you go, then.
[SHIRAYUKI] Well, he does
have a valid point.
I guess I'll have to convince
him I'm not any kind of threat.
Hey. What the--?
No-- What're you--?
Sorry to disappoint, but
I don't usually carry poison.
[MITSUHIDE laughing]
She sure got you there, Zen.
[ZEN laughing]
[sighs]
I'm sorry about that.
My name's Zen.
And mine is Shirayuki.
It's lovely to
meet you, Shirayuki.
However, I think you're at
least partially responsible
for my less than
graceful landing.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
[ZEN] No one lives in this
house, but we spend time here.
So, the one getting beaten at
chess over there is Mitsuhide,
The one doing the
beating is Kiki.
Zen, how do you know I'm losing
when you aren't even paying
attention to the game?
I can just tell.
I'm shellacking you.
[MITSUHIDE growls]
Okay, you're all fixed up now.
Wow, you've got impressive
skills, Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I've been at this a while.
I did tell you
I was an herbalist.
Yes, you did.
So, why would a talented
herbalist run away from home?
The reason's not important.
Excuse me, I need some air.
Hey, why did you come with me?
I couldn't let you go into these
woods all by your lonesome.
That would be quite
ungentlemanly.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oddball.
I became very comfortable
in the mountains and forests
while studying
to be an herbalist.
[SHIRAYUKI sighs]
The time and air here
seem to flow differently
than they do in town.
I actually like it much better.
[ZEN]
I couldn't agree more.
[SHIRAYUKI] Look who isn't
all bluff and bluster.
Ow!
That really hurts.
Oh, looks like
your hair's caught.
You have a strand that's
longer than the others.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh? Oh...
I must've missed
that piece earlier.
Uh, hey, Zen, will you
cut it off for me?
[ZEN]
Huh.
It doesn't have to be straight.
[ZEN]
Possibly.
But I'll only do it if you
answer a question for me.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
[ZEN] Did cutting your hair
have something to do
with why you ran away from home?
If you tell me the reason,
maybe then I can help you.
You're a terrible person.
[ZEN chuckles]
[ZEN] You were ordered
to be a concubine?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes, by a very famous boy.
He was born with a silver
spoon in his mouth,
but he learned to speak
in the red-light district.
He thought my hair was unusual,
and wanted to keep it
for himself like a prize.
If I had obeyed his order,
it would've been just
like he was buying an apple
at the fruit seller.
Shirayuki--
[SHIRAYUKI]
So that's why,
I thought that I'd give him at
least part of what he wanted,
and I left my hair behind.
[ZEN laughing]
That was ingenious thinking!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Good job getting away
from that dunce.
It's your lucky red, after all.
What do you mean by that?
Well...
Color has meaning.
And red is supposed
to represent fate.
You may not like it much now,
but your red might lead
to something good when
you least expect it.
Wow, you have an
amazing outlook, Zen.
Oh! Some respect!
[MITSUHIDE]
How 'bout that.
Not so suspicious anymore.
Yup, but it doesn't hurt
that Zen has taken
quite a shine to her.
[ZEN]
What's this?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, no.
That's the ribbon
I had tied to my hair.
[ZEN]
So you're from Tanbarun, I see.
Meaning the person who
dropped off this basket
traveled all the way to
the border just to find you.
He is a determined fellow.
I'll give him that much.
[SHIRAYUKI chuckles]
Right?
This isn't a joke!
How bad was it that you were
forced to flee the kingdom?
I had to leave
because of who he is.
Someone powerful.
The first prince of Tanbarun.
[ZEN]
Raj?
That royal moron?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Are you all right?
Yes, that's him.
He's so stupid that even all the
neighboring countries know it.
I don't blame you for running.
He doubtlessly had people
everywhere tearing apart
all the border crossing records.
Do you really believe
he would go that far?
If there's something
he wants bad enough,
he probably already assumes
it belongs to him.
Even if it means caging it.
He's awful.
[ZEN]
Hm?
It's starting to go bad.
This red is no good
to anyone now.
I'm just kidding.
Zen.
How uncouth of you.
That's her apple, Zen.
Why don't you go get your own?
What're you--
[ZEN coughing]
[MITSUHIDE] You should either
talk or eat. Don't do both.
[ZEN]
Nobody asked you.
Stay out of it!
Well, now you're
just being rude.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen!
What now?!
I was being foolish. I'm sorry.
Shirayuki, I would put that
apple down if I were you.
Kiki, Mitsuhide. Don't get mad.
[BOTH]
Zen!
[MITSUHIDE]
What happened?
[KIKI]
Zen!
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's poisoned!
Can you help him?!
Give me a moment!
It's no good. I can't prepare
one with what I have.
If I don't hurry...
[MESSENGER]
My, my. It looks as though
someone else has tasted the
apple instead of Miss Shirayuki.
Who're you?
Oh, no.
[MESSENGER]
Hmm.
This changes things.
How could you do this?!
Calm yourself, miss. A certain
someone possesses the antidote.
I trust now you will
come with me quietly?
[RAJ]
Oh, so you made it!
I have to say,
it's quite a surprise.
I didn't believe that red hair
you left behind was real.
Uh, so what about the antidote?
[RAJ]
All in good time.
Just so you know,
Miss Shirayuki,
the world is very judgmental.
The fact that I graciously
courted you and you ran away
has since made me a
laughingstock all over Tanbarun
and in the royal palace.
Thanks to you, public opinion
of me has plummeted drastically.
However, despite my
shame, the unanimous opinion
is that it's nobody else's
fault but your own.
Understand.
We have to wipe the filth
from my good name.
And in order to do that, you'll
have to become my concubine.
I would never dream of causing
a woman embarrassment.
Not even a lowly commoner
such as yourself.
You can thank me for
my generosity, now.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Are-- Are you kidding me?
And will you please focus?
What's more important
is the antidote!
My friend is very sick, and
he needs to have it right away!
Oh, that's right, of course!
If you agree to my proposal,
I will have it delivered
here for him immediately.
Or, dearest...
...would you prefer I give
him another apple, instead.
[ZEN]
Color has meaning.
And red is supposed
to represent fate.
You may not like it much now,
but your red might lead
to something good when
you least expect it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Lead to something good?
The only thing I led
Zen to is poison.
[RAJ]
I have to say,
now that I can see how
truly beautiful you are,
I think I should keep
you very close to me.
Wha--? Why'd you--?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, my apologies.
Fine, Prince Raj.
Take me if you wish.
But you should know
what you're getting.
[SOLDIER A]
Wait, stay back!
--[thud]
--[BOTH gasp]
[RAJ]
Huh?
I object!
Zen!
You wretch!
[ZEN] You will stop spewing
such disgusting filth
that sullies that poor girl's
ears, you boorish pig!
[RAJ whimpering]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen!
Shirayuki, hey. Tie this for me?
Wait, before that,
what about your body?
Are you okay?
I've spent the last few years
building up an immunity
to different poisons.
Yeah, but you--
[RAJ]
Aha!
So you were the one who took
a bite of the poisoned apple.
Well, that was
rather unfortunate.
I was planning on
immobilizing Miss Shirayuki
so I could take her
back home with me.
Why am I not surprised that
you were behind a bad apple?
Best mind your manners
around me, country boy!
Peasants like you should
show more respect to royalty.
[ZEN]
Oh, pardon me,
sensitive, delicate first
monarch of Tanbarun,
I mean, Prince Raj Schenazade.
[RAJ]
Heh?
[ZEN] I'm not one for
formal introductions, but...
I recognize that crest.
[ZEN]
As well you should, imbecile.
Meet the Second Prince
of Clarines kingdom,
I'm Zen Wisteria.
A... prince?
[gasps]
Did he say prince?
Zen, please calm down.
Get a hold of yourself!
Wait! Do you know who I am?
What's one plus one?
It's true, Shirayuki.
But I never actually thought
I'd be poisoned by anyone,
much less a half-wit prince
from a neighboring kingdom.
Could mean war.
No. Besides, you...
You have no proof whatsoever
that I poisoned the apple!
Oh, I think we have plenty.
Yeah, we'll see what's what
when we make an
official inquiry, liar.
No! Please wait, I--
Well then, why don't we
make a trade, Prince Moron?
If you don't want your
deceptive actions
to be a matter of public record,
then swear you will never
come near Shirayuki again,
or even dare to say
her name out loud.
How do you know Shirayuki?
[RAJ yelping]
Okay, okay! I promise!
Please! Cross my heart!
Shirayuki,
surely you have a few things
you'd like to say to him.
If you want to air
some grievances,
you should do it now.
Here, Prince Raj.
To get your strength back,
since you're so shocked,
you can't even move. Also...
[RAJ]
Yes?
Give Zen the antidote, now.
[RAJ]
Yes, ma'am.
[RAJ screaming]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank you.
For what, Shirayuki?
Because you saved me
from danger, Zen.
But I'm sorry.
It would seem that I'm
only poisonous to you.
Is that supposed to be a joke?
Because I was poisoned by an
apple, and you're as red as one,
is that what you mean?
No, not really.
[KIKI]
Don't worry.
It's not something for
which you need to apologize.
Zen made the choice to
eat the apple himself,
but we all should've been
a lot more careful about it.
That's all.
Although, Mitsuhide carried on
like the end of
the world was near
and started to weep
like a child.
Hey, shut up, Kiki!
[KIKI]
So tragic.
[ZEN]
Okay, okay.
Next time I get fruit,
I'll have Mitsuhide test
it out before I eat it.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh, what's that, now?
[ZEN laughing]
[ZEN]
Shirayuki,
do you remember what I said
to you in the forest?
I meant every word.
And I truly hope our fate
brought us together
for something good.
We both happened to be
in the same place
for very different reasons,
and we saved each other.
Maybe poison isn't always bad.
Maybe our meeting
wasn't a fluke,
but instead the beginning
of a new chapter.
I guess it's up to you, now.
Is that true? I can
choose my fate for myself?
Of course.
That's exactly what I'm doing,
and nobody's going to stop me.
You can follow one path, or you
can go a different direction,
neither of which is wrong.
Zen, you--
I what?
You know, I really do
like the way you think.
But it's not how I think.
It's how I live.
So, what's your answer?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Well, it's literally my story.
If I had my way,
on the path in front of
us after this encounter,
you could hear the sound of
pages turning in this story,
and they would echo like my
footsteps, moving towards...
Destiny.
[ZEN]
And now, I have.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Clarines is a lovely place.
[MIHAYA]
What a valiant effort.
[ZEN]
What? Shirayuki's not here?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, yes.
There's a reason I've decided
to stay in this country.
[MIHAYA] Are you finally
done running, Princess?