[SHIRAYUKI]
I want to know it.
See how the rest of
you live in Clarines.
Find out where I belong.
That's the place
where I'm going.
The place where I'll be at home.
[ZEN]
Well, when you're there.
I hope I'll still be able
to see you anyway.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki?
Stay there, I'll come down.
[SHIRAYUKI]
No! I'll climb up to you!
Reach out!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[BOTH grunt]
Well, that was unexpected.
How'd you even know
I was up here?
I noticed someone on the
balcony, and knew it was you.
But I... I assumed
you'd gone back inside.
You said my name.
What could I do?
Walk away?
[ZEN gasps]
[ZEN]
Did something happen?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes, kind of.
[ZEN]
I thought so.
[SHIRAYUKI]
When I look to the future,
I listen to dreams
echoing in my heart.
And I long for the day
when I'm not the only
one who can hear them.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki, what happened?
Does it have to do
with my brother?
[ZEN]
Please tell me.
What did he say to you during
your meeting, earlier?
[SHIRAYUKI]
It sounded a lot like a warning.
As if he was telling
me to consider
whether I deserved to
be here with you.
[gasps]
Oh, I see.
Now his recent behavior
makes sense. Sorry.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh! Why?
[ZEN] Because, no matter
what my brother does,
I can't hate him.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I know.
Wait, that can't be all.
He had to have said something
worse than a warning
after he made me leave.
I swear he has no mercy.
Well, even if he did, it's fine.
It's not like I need anyone
to go beat their brother up
on my behalf.
Uh?
[exhales]
Ah.
Shouldn't have done that.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
I let go too quickly.
I must admit, I was really
enjoying holding you.
[ZEN]
Uh?
Uh...
Listen. I have a story.
It's about my brother.
Do you want to hear it?
I do.
He was the firstborn,
and as such, a priority.
I, however, was always
in his shadow.
[ZEN]
On his 17th birthday,
he was asked what he wanted.
Now, what do I want as my gift?
A castle would be nice.
One bordering Lido
and Sui territories.
Are you certain, Sire?
For as I understand it,
their lords have been
feuding for ages!
[OFFICIAL B]
Are you thinking
of mediating between
them, highness?
[IZANA]
Of course not.
[OFFICIAL A] Then... why would
you want a castle there?
Because the land is beautiful,
and its value extremely high.
[NOBLES murmur]
[ZEN] It took a while for me to
understand what was happening.
I was too young.
But soon, to get into my
brother's good graces,
the lords of Lido and Sui
sent him copious amounts
of money and goods.
How very generous of you.
[ZEN]
And my brother happily accepted,
parlaying the gifts into
ample construction funds.
[ZEN]
Before too long,
retainers from both men had come
to speak with him in secret.
In order to assist you with
financing the castle,
the lord of Lido has been
unfairly taking money
from his people.
And it's the same in Sui.
I beg of you, please
reconsider this venture!
Why aren't you
complaining to them?
[RETAINERS exhale]
Highness, please!
[ZEN] Gossip about
my brother's actions
quickly began to spread
around the castle.
I believed he was
playing a cruel game.
You've been standing there
long enough. Speak.
[KID ZEN]
There's a rumor.
The Sui retainer has
lost his position
because he's been banished.
[IZANA]
Sounds right.
The one from Lido hasn't
been around lately, either.
Makes one wonder what happened.
[KID ZEN]
Do you 'wonder', though?
I'll tell you what, Zen.
Let's go see how the
castle's coming along.
[KID ZEN]
Uh.
We can make a couple
of stops along the way.
[ZEN] True to his word, he
took me with him to visit
the two lords, and he told
them both the same story.
[IZANA]
I thought you should know,
the other lord is greedily
usurping his people's money
in a blatant attempt
to curry favor with me.
I'm not sure that's
the wisest of moves.
What good could he
possibly be to me
if he renders his
people impoverished?
It's truly a disgrace.
Only an unworthy leader would
make such a foolish decision.
[ZEN] Each one thought
they could take advantage
of my brother's seeming
dislike for the other.
So, they stopped
overtly extorting money,
turning to even more
unlawful tactics.
Which was precisely
what Izana expected.
He secretly investigated
the crimes of the two lords
and their accomplices,
eventually removing them all.
[ZEN gasps]
[IZANA] Lords who allow
their people to rot
should know the same fate.
Let them die in the shadows.
[ZEN gasping]
[ZEN]
Both lords lost everything.
My brother quickly appointed
their two former retainers
as their successors.
I'm pleased to say
these gentlemen
have been well taken
care of at the castle.
[ZEN] Izana allotted the
vast amounts of tribute
he had received
from the two lords
to be used as funds
for both lands.
He never spent a single coin.
[ZEN]
I apologize, Lord Brother.
I never considered you had
a plan and just assumed
you were using the lords
as a means of amusement.
[IZANA] Well, who says I wasn't?
I had a great time.
Aren't you worried, though?
They could be holding a
grudge against you, now.
I'm sure they are. Revenge
on me is probably imminent.
Don't say that!
If I have no one to protect me
from danger when the time comes,
then that will be a reflection
of a failed legacy.
Zen.
If you do not make those
around you recognize you
as the king's son, you will
never be aware of it yourself.
[ZEN]
He was right.
This man was going to be
the king of Clarines.
I wanted to become
a person worthy
and deserving of a
place by his side.
Nothing mattered more to me.
[ZEN] I'm sorry, it's
gotten pretty late.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I guess so.
[ZEN] Shirayuki, there's,
uh, there's one more thing
I needed to talk to you about.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Which is?
[ZEN] Raj said something fairly
outrageous at the party.
Oh, no, what did he say?
Well, you won't like it.
He announced that I...
That I was thinking
of you as my fiancée.
[ZEN] I don't know if
anyone took him seriously,
but it might be
uncomfortable from now on.
Everyone around here
will be watching you,
and wondering if there's
any truth to it.
[SHIRAYUKI] Then, this means...
I can stay in the castle!
Wait, but what about you
and the Laxdo incident?
Don't be concerned.
Those men will soon recover.
Right. You don't have
to worry about me, Zen.
I don't mind what
anyone might say.
[ZEN]
Uh!
I mean, it's not like it's
true. Who cares, right?
[gasps] What'd I say?
[ZEN] In that case, it doesn't
matter if everyone's watching.
You should just do as you
please, and be true to yourself.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes.
[ZEN] I know it's easier
said than done,
and it doesn't apply
to everything.
You may slip up sometimes,
but you know that's okay.
Everyone does.
I'll take my advice, too.
And remember, I'm
always on your side.
[KAI] Shirayuki and
the prince are together?!
All right!
Keep your voice down, Kai.
It doesn't make sense;
they don't seem as though
they're anything more
than just good friends.
Come on, where'd you
hear this juicy tidbit?
You have to tell me, please!
I heard it from the guards who
were working the tea party.
They said that prince
who was visiting from
Tanbarun declared it.
Oh, that guy. I wonder...
How he would know?
[SHILA]
Seems like he knows Shirayuki
and the prince pretty well.
So, next we'll be taking a
tour of the medical buildings?
Are you feeling all
right, Prince Raj?
I'm fine, don't you worry!
Anyway...
they look just wonderful!
From the very best
buildings are borne
the very best
medicines, naturally!
Tanbarun could learn
from this example!
Right, Sakaki?
Uh! Yes, sir.
I'm so honored by
your kind words.
Well then, please come inside.
[RAJ]
No, that's all right!
We have thoughtlessly taken
enough of your valuable time
already, dear Madame.
Think nothing of it.
Prince Izana
specifically requested
that I show you around the
entire castle grounds.
Then I'm grateful to you
both for that generous
and considerate offer.
Excuse me a moment.
Sakaki, you check it out first!
Yes, but why me?
Use your head, fool!
Didn't you hear them say
that girl was working
as an herbalist in there?
I can't risk running into her!
That's true, and we have caused
her enough problems already.
Right. Anyway.
No good can possibly come of us
meeting again, even by accident.
And I'm positive Shirayuki
feels the same way.
[GARAK]
Pardon, Prince Raj?
Is everything all right?
Yes. Please excuse me.
[clears throat] Are we clear?
Yes.
All right, let us continue
our fascinating tour!
--[SAKAKI sighs]
--Sakaki!
Right away, sir.
--[door opens]
--This room is nice.
[RAJ] What a splendid
facility you have!
[GARAK] Um. That's just
the storage area.
[RAJ]
Storage!
[SAKAKI]
This room is nice, too.
[RAJ]
Magical! I've never seen finer!
[GARAK]
Yes, thank you.
[ZEN] Do you think you can
finish by this evening?
Yes.
Excellent, then that will
be the last of the checks.
[SERVANT A]
Thank you very much.
[ZEN sighs]
Boy, Zen.
The days feel a lot longer
than 24 hours lately.
Oh, be quiet.
Kiki, what's up after this?
You get to see
Prince Raj off, finally.
Very good.
I'll see you there
in a bit, then.
[KIKI]
Have fun, Zen.
[MITSUHIDE]
Don't be too late.
[OBI]
Master!
Are you heading over
to see the Miss now?
[ZEN] No, Shirayuki's
working at the moment.
Huh.
Oh, by the way, have
you seen my brother?
[OBI] No, you have
business with him?
I just wanted to
have a little chat.
[RAJ groans] Oh, I'm glad
that's finally over.
I wouldn't get comfortable
just yet, Highness.
We're not leaving the castle
until this evening.
Yes, I know!
[SAKAKI]
Oh, again?
Ow! I'm not faking it!
I've been so wracked
with worry and stress
it's making my stomach hurt.
You should've mentioned
that to me earlier.
Are you serious?!
It's just a stomachache.
I can't afford to let
anyone here think
I might be vulnerable.
I understand.
At least let me go fetch
some medicine for you.
Wait, whatever you do,
don't say it's for me.
[SAKAKI]
As you wish.
[groans]
[sighs]
So, all that's left to do
is take this down to the
treatment room, right?
[RYU]
Yeah.
I'll start heading
over there now, then.
[RYU]
Thank you.
[door closes]
[RYU] Something seems
a little off with her.
[GUARD A] Is it the girl
close to Prince Zen?
[GUARD B] Yes, the one who
has the bright red hair.
[GUARD A]
Oh, her.
I don't think it's been
set in stone yet, though.
It might as well be,
she seems awfully close
to Mitsuhide and Kiki
from what I've seen.
[SHIRAYUKI] This is just
like Zen said it would be.
[ZEN] But it might be
uncomfortable from now on.
[SHIRAYUKI]
It doesn't matter. Who cares?
Lord Brother.
May I have a word with you?
[ZEN]
Izana?!
[IZANA] Come, Zen. Let's spar
a little, and we can talk.
Do you mean right this minute?
I've been feeling
a bit restless.
Following that little twerp
around makes me tense.
Besides, I think you want more
than just to chat, right?
[ZEN grunts]
[IZANA grunts]
You have the floor.
Start talking.
[ZEN grunts]
Well, for starters.
Why do you treat Shirayuki
like a nuisance
when you don't know her yet?!
Because I'm too
busy at the moment
to play 'getting to know you'
with a girl who's
clearly a distraction.
[ZEN] Too busy to bother
learning even one thing
before writing her off?
[gasps] Well, look who
finally found his voice!
I never needed my voice before.
[IZANA]
That's my point. I knew it.
It took no time whatsoever
to figure this out.
You've fallen for her
hard, and you know it.
Although, in the end,
it's irrelevant.
We can't always get what
our hearts want, Zen.
There are other girls out
there who have more value
and political worth.
People will want to see
if she has something to offer
Clarines besides unusual hair.
Once they realize she doesn't,
you'll be the laughingstock
of the entire kingdom.
[ZEN grunts]
[IZANA grunts]
You're rather off your
game today. Pity.
Prepare yourself.
Because Shirayuki has a way
of taking preconceived
notions about her
and proving them wrong.
I'm bored with this, now.
Come on, let's go back.
[ZEN] Lord Brother! You should
know you're wrong about her.
And having that girl in my life
is not going to divert
me from my path.
Then leave her behind.
[ZEN grunts]
[ZEN yells]
[panting]
[ZEN]
Never.
You're supposed to watch Zen,
and yet you allowed him to
bring a red headed diversion
into our lives.
I'm starting to think it's
because I was watching him.
[IZANA] Wonderful, it looks like
we have two impertinent mouths.
[MITSUHIDE] Guessing Zen
finally stood up to him,
and said something
"impertinent."
Our little prince is
starting to grow up.
[RAJ groaning]
What in the world could be
holding Sakaki up so long?
At this rate, my stomach
will rip itself open!
[RAJ gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
It looks like you're
working hard in Clarines.
This seems like
a very nice place.
I am, and yes, it is.
Uh... Well, excuse me.
[groaning]
Do you need some help?
No, no, nothing. I'm fine.
What's this? Is it medicine?
Yes, but it's specific.
[RAJ] You mean, they asked
you to bring it down to me?
Wait. What are you doing?
That's not for you!
[RAJ] Mm? Isn't this the
remedy I asked them for?
I know nothing about
a remedy for you!
Well, I told him not to
say that it was for me!
I'm taking this now!
[gasps]
[RAJ]
Uh...
That contained a
topical treatment!
It's for flesh wounds!
What?! So, it wasn't
a stomach medicine?
I said no!
[RAJ] Uh. Oh, well,
that could've ended badly.
[sighs] Well, I can't
really fault you
for thinking it was yours.
I should have been more
careful carrying it around.
You are royalty, though,
and in the jurisdiction
of another country.
You need to take responsibility
for your own safety.
One would imagine
my status as a prince
would be enough for you to
watch your tongue around me.
You're not supposed
to say stuff like that!
If you want me to respect
you as though I'm proud
of the ruler of my country,
then rule my country
like a prince I can be proud of.
You can't say stuff
like that, either!
[SHIRAYUKI]
You may very well be right,
but as someone from Tanbarun,
I think it's a
reasonable request.
[gasps] Are you serious?
[RAJ]
Ooh! That was rhetorical.
I don't need any more
insults, thank you!
[SAKAKI]
Your highness!
You shouldn't be wandering
the grounds alone!
You were too slow,
and I got bored!
Now, where's my medicine?
They need to examine you
before prescribing something.
[SHIRAYUKI] If you want, I can
take you to the treatment room.
[RAJ]
I think not!
[SAKAKI grunts]
Wait for me!
[RAJ] No! I don't have time to
wait around for you anymore!
The chief herbalist isn't
going to like this.
[IZANA]
No, I imagine she won't.
Not after I tell her what I saw.
You have to realize by now
you'd be much better
off with Prince Raj.
Life for you here could be
unpleasant with me around.
You know that, right?
Prince Izana.
I have no intention of ever
returning to Tanbarun.
[IZANA]
Is that so?
I'm rather disappointed
to hear it.
You refuse to retreat?
Absolutely.
[IZANA] Direct eye contact,
too? Aren't you something?
So, tell me Princess.
Have you come to dislike it?
No, I never will.
It's the country
where I met Zen.
What strange children you are.
You don't think she'll show
up at the sendoff, do you?
[SAKAKI]
Are you worried about something?
[RAJ] Sakaki, please bow once
toward the castle in my stead.
What? Why me?
Just do what I ask you!
I'm trying not to lose face!
Right...
[bell tolls]
[RAJ gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
This is the path I've chosen.
[SHIRAYUKI] And I found
a beacon to guide me, now.
So I will keep moving forward.
And I won't let go.
[SHIRAYUKI]
No matter what,
we'll always have the
wind at our backs.
[MITSUHIDE] He was still
so young back then.
Barely more than a child.
[ATRI]
Prince Zen.
[MITSUHIDE]
Yet he bore a burden
which many adults
couldn't carry.