A few herbs for the final touch.
There.
[knocking]
Yes, please come in!
Good morning, Shirayuki!
Here, I have your
fresh-baked bread.
That looks great!
[WOMAN]
I'll leave it right here.
I have something for you, too!
[WOMAN gasps]
That smells so good.
It looks like a cure-all.
This stuff will even
make your skin smoother!
That'd be nice!
[WOMAN laughing]
Do you enjoy living
in Clarines so far?
Yes.
In fact, I thought I'd start
looking for a job today.
Sounds like a smart plan.
After all, if we wanna eat,
we have to work, don't we?
Right!
Good luck! Have a great day!
Thanks! You, too!
[SHIRAYUKI] Wistal, the capital
city of the kingdom of Clarines,
and right now, my sanctuary.
Because of my unique hair,
the prince of Tanbarun tried
to force me to be his concubine.
So I fled my home country
to start a new life
in this kingdom.
I had planned to go along with
whatever fate decided for me,
but Zen, the Second
Prince of Clarines,
helped me to discover that
I still have a choice.
So, here I am.
In the country I choose.
In the city I choose.
On the road I choose.
[SHIRAYUKI]
A gardener. A painter.
A carriage repair worker.
These aren't right,
but this might be.
You're an herbalist?
[SHIRAYUKI] Yes, and I would
very much like to work here.
If I can.
[PHARMACIST]
Hmm...
Unfortunately, we don't
need anyone, now.
Besides, that hair.
You can't judge someone
just based on her looks, dear.
What would our customers
think if they heard you?
[PHARMACIST]
Yes, you're right. Very sorry.
[SHIRAYUKI] They have so
many rare medicinal herbs
that I can't get back home.
Wow.
Not only that,
but they have varieties
I've never seen before.
[PHARMACIST'S WIFE]
Thank you for waiting.
Is this closer to
what you were wanting?
That boy. Is he
a regular customer?
Indeed.
He's still young,
but he's already a very
respected court herbalist.
Oh, really?
Yes, listen closely,
not everyone knows this,
but only the most knowledgeable,
gifted and skillful herbalists
will ever be considered
for a valued position
working in the court.
Clarines is a country
with deep pockets,
and they will assist
talented people.
If they're talented enough
to do the job, that is.
Right.
In medical study,
Clarines is much more
advanced than most kingdoms.
Here's the information on how
you can become a
court herbalist.
If you can successfully pass
the annual test they offer,
you'll be eligible to
work in Wistal Castle
as a new apprentice.
Uh. Thank you!
Please come back soon!
If you're truly interested,
then I think you should
try taking the exam.
But, be warned it is
rather difficult.
You, there!
I do beg your pardon,
but I've come here to
see Kiki or Mitsuhide
from the royal guards.
[SHILA]
Hmm.
[KAI]
Uh!
That's her!
It is. You're that girl!
My apologies, miss.
We've only just been informed
that you're a guest
of Prince Zen's.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki!
[KAI, SHILA]
Prince Zen, sir!
Uh...
You... were outside
the castle? Why?
I needed some exercise.
Can't risk getting outta shape
doing all that paperwork.
[SHIRAYUKI]
So basically you snuck out
in order to avoid
your royal duties?
[ZEN]
You caught me.
It was also an excuse
to see you again.
And now, I have.
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Zen!
Where are you?
So, what're you doing here?
I assume it's for
something specific?
Um, yes.
You wanted me to be sure
and let you know
whenever I was going
to leave the capitol.
Well...
Great, let's go!
We'll leave now!
Do me a favor, boys,
tell Mitsuhide I had
to run an errand.
[KAI, SHILA]
Sir! Yessir!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Excuse me!
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Zen! Where'd you go?!
[ZEN]
Mount Koto?
Yes.
That's the mountain
beyond the ocean.
What precisely are you
looking for there?
Many medicinal herbs
are native to the area.
I wanna stock up and
study more about medicine,
so the town pharmacist told me
of a few promising places,
mentioning this one
as especially good.
[ZEN]
Huh.
Why do you still need to study?
Aren't you already an herbalist?
I am, but I'm only ever
going to get better
if I keep on learning.
Plus, I wanna know everything.
Great.
Then why don't you come with
me to the forest tomorrow?
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Clarines is a lovely place.
[ZEN]
Huh?
Just so charming and peaceful.
[BOY]
It's bright red.
Mommy, Mommy! Can you
tell me why is it so red?
Look at that lady's
hair! See how red?
How come? Why?
[MOTHER]
Shh. Stop bothering her.
Be quiet and eat your food.
That's enough, now.
It looks like a
shiny apple, right?
[BOY]
Mh-hm.
Wanna eat it! Mommy,
mommy! Apples!
I want to eat apples now!
Let's go eat some!
[MOTHER]
Uh, okay.
[BOY]
Yay! All the apples!
[ALL laughing]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Wow, it's so diverse!
Because it's a hub for folk
from various countries.
All kinds of cultures
blend here.
[WINE SELLER]
Well, Prince Zen!
Greetings. Just got a
shipment of new wine in.
You interested?
Not today. Some
other time, though.
[WINE SELLER]
Yes, sir.
Who's he?
A wine merchant I met
in town a while ago.
Since then, I purchase
his wares for my soldiers.
Oh.
[SHIRAYUKI] Zen, why do
you keep leaving the castle?
[ZEN]
Hm?
[SHIRAYUKI] Prince Raj
always orders his servants
to bring the things
he wants to his castle.
He doesn't ever lift a finger.
When they don't bring
him what he wants,
he supposedly throws tantrums.
The entire kingdom
thinks it's ridiculous.
[ZEN]
I can understand why.
Before, when we were
talking on the way here,
you said you thought this
country was charming.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mh-hm.
I think so, too.
I'm still learning.
I feel like there must
be mountains of charm
I have yet to discover.
And so, I want to know
everything about it.
I want to keep learning.
[SHIRAYUKI] Good herbs are
needed for good medicines.
And good land is
needed for good herbs.
I wanna find out even
more about this land,
and all the herbs
that grow here.
I daresay,
you and I are somewhat alike.
--[bell ringing]
--[BOATMAN] Final Call!
I have to go!
[BOATMAN]
Everyone on board!
[CROWD yelling]
I hope you find
some useful herbs!
Thanks!
I'll be back before
the sun goes down!
[MAN A]
Did you see that red hair?
Yeah, it's very special.
I'm certain we could
get a nice price for it!
[MAN A yelps]
[MEN whimpering]
[sighs]
These will make great remedies.
[MAN]
Hello, Rosylocks.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Well, sir, you're
in high spirits.
[ZEN]
Hmph.
Leaving the castle today
was quite inspiring.
Glad to hear it, sir.
Perhaps it can inspire you
to finish that paperwork.
Shirayuki's working
hard out there.
Fine!
[BOTH gasp]
The Shirayuki Effect. Amazing.
[MAN]
Good, you're awake.
My name's Mihaya.
We met earlier. Remember?
I think we might have
different definitions of "met."
I assume... there's an agenda?
Well if there wasn't, you
wouldn't be here right now.
[MIHAYA]
Tell me.
What do you think I should
do about a rare treasure
even a prince couldn't get
his pampered hands on?
Whomever it's presented to,
would pay a handsome
reward for such a find.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What?
[MIHAYA]
For example,
a fiery, red-haired beauty
decorated with natural jewels.
Just imagine.
So are you saying you're
planning to sell me?
No need to be vulgar.
It sounds ugly when
you put it that way.
There are tons of rich people
who have very strange taste.
Why would you even think
of something like that?
Of course... Heh.
I could also wait patiently
until your hair grows out more.
I think I would enjoy the
pleasure of your company
a great deal during
the down time.
Great. It's settled.
[gasps]
[ZEN]
What? Shirayuki's not here?
[WOMAN] No, I brought bread
to her room this morning,
but she was gone.
Also, last night, her light
inside was never turned on.
I certainly hope
nothing bad happened
to that sweet, sweet girl.
Oh?
Hungry? Here.
[MIHAYA yelps]
Wench!
No!
[MIHAYA] She must've been
sawing away at the rope all day.
This girl is different.
Locked.
[MIHAYA]
Ah, welcome back.
[MIHAYA] I think you might
be looking for these.
You're going to need them
to get out of here.
[SHIRAYUKI]
How did he get up there?
I feel compelled to remind you
you're up on a
mountain, Rosylocks.
Even if you escaped,
you would have no idea
how to find your way back.
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're wrong.
Because I already know
where I need to go.
And I am not looking
for your company.
So find somebody else to sell!
[gasps]
Are you finally done
running, Princess?
[SHIRAYUKI]
For now.
[MIHAYA]
Heh.
Then it sounds like you're
ready to let me catch you.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Come on, please work!
Curse you!
What the--?
[SHIRAYUKI] I burned herbs
with paralyzing effects,
so you're gonna lose the feeling
in your body for a while.
Have a nice rest!
[SHIRAYUKI] He was on
the second floor earlier.
He obviously didn't
want me going up there.
There must be a way out!
[SHIRAYUKI panting]
[SHIRAYUKI]
There're no bars!
[yelps]
[MIHAYA]
What a valiant effort.
But... bad... news.
Sadly, this is the end.
I'm afraid those
herbs you burned
didn't have much
of an effect on me.
[MIHAYA] You might as well
stop fighting right now.
Suppose you do escape
me and this mountain.
You'll just get chased
by someone else
with worse intentions.
Wouldn't it be much safer in
the care of nobility or royalty?
You'd be protected,
and live in luxury.
Doesn't that sound
vastly more appealing?
So, what say you, Red?
I say no.
I think I'll take
a different path.
That's the wrong answer,
you're coming with me!
[gasps]
Back off, bastard!
[groaning]
[ZEN panting]
So, Shirayuki, wasn't this
supposed to be a day trip?
Zen.
Are you hurt?
Oh, no, no. I'm all right.
That's good.
[MIHAYA coughing]
Heh. You have your own guardian.
My luck.
I wanted to have
that job for myself.
I could present her
almost anywhere,
and I'd finally make some money.
Was that your plan all along?
[MIHAYA]
Yes, it was.
This mansion here?
It belonged to my family.
Our vacation home
when we were nobility.
[SHIRAYUKI] Ah. No wonder
you knew it so well.
Today, I have to live in hiding.
Like a dirty, stray mongrel.
This house was once lavish, but
that was a very long time ago.
Social status and family name
can be swallowed up
by darkness in a moment.
Your self-proclaimed elegance
and fancy clothes won't save you
if you found yourself penniless.
You could wind up filthy,
and shamed, just like me.
No. I refuse to live
like this a moment longer.
I swear. I'm going
to be rich again.
I don't care what I have
to do to make it happen.
That's why I thought you'd
be a good insurance policy
for me, Red.
You're a guarantee.
That's enough.
I don't wanna hear any more.
You can keep your offensive
metaphors for her to yourself.
Shirayuki will not be a pawn.
For you or anyone, got it?
So your name's Shirayuki.
Do not speak her name!
Calm down.
Are you her father or something?
You are seriously asking for it.
Shirayuki, quick question.
Was this guy alone?
Uh... I don't know.
I didn't see anyone else.
If he's by himself, we can just
take him down the mountain.
We won't have to escort him
all the way to the castle.
We'll hand him over to
officials down at the base.
Castle?
What am I dealing
with? Who are you?
[ZEN]
Zen.
Huh...
Wait... as in Zen, the
Second Prince of Clarines?
As well as Shirayuki's friend.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Excuse me!
Sir, please apply this
balm to his injuries.
You never told me, Red.
Where is that place
you mentioned
you wanted to go earlier? Alone?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
[GUARD A]
Let's go!
Start walking, boy!
[SHIRAYUKI] From what
the officials indicated,
Mihaya doesn't seem to be
connected to any bandits.
He's working solo.
[ZEN]
Yes.
[SHIRAYUKI]
But just in case,
I'll be much more wary of
my surroundings from now on.
Good.
Are... you angry?
[ZEN]
No.
Fine!
Then will you please make
eye contact? Ten seconds!
Look, you came to rescue me.
I don't have the
right words, but...
Thank you for--
That's all I needed.
Five seconds.
[ZEN]
I'll admit, I was a bit upset.
Not with you, though.
It's hard to explain, but
I was really mad at myself.
The truth?
Exploring life outside the
castle, I learned a great deal.
But after learning these things,
I realized I'm not doing enough.
Zen.
[ZEN] Shirayuki, what was
the answer to the question
that mountain monkey
asked you earlier?
What is the place you're
planning on going by yourself?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ah. Oh, yes.
There's a reason I've decided
to stay in this country.
I want to know it.
See how the rest of
you live in Clarines.
Find out where I belong.
That's the place
where I'm going.
The place where I'll be at home.
Well, when you're there,
I hope I'll still be able
to see you anyway.
Shirayuki. Thank you, too.
I'm happy that you're all right.
[SHIRAYUKI]
So, here I am.
In the country I choose.
In the city I choose.
On the road I choose.
Even if things get in my way,
at least my path is
within my own power.
No matter what, I know I'll
always have the wind at my back.
[SHIRAYUKI] Seeing all of
Clarines would be incredible!
[HARUKA] She'll have
expectations and take advantage.
[SHIRAYUKI] I thought you would
like to know that I'm applying.
[OBI]
Oh, I see.
The redhead is
apparently familiar
with the dear, sweet prince.
Heh.
[HARUKA]
Red is a vulgar color.