[SHIRAYUKI] True human
value can't be measured
by social status.
It's measured by one's
depth of character.
Meanwhile, you've shown you
have no character at all!
[SHIKITO] The viscount tried
to sabotage the test,
so I had to arrest him.
He is out of the picture.
Unfortunately, the
assistant was injured.
[ZEN]
Show me where you're hurt.
It's not like I was ever
gonna try to hide this.
I know how mad you'd be at me.
[ZEN]
Idiot.
[gasping]
[ZEN] I-I don't know
what just came over me!
I'm sorry. Please forgive me!
[ZEN] Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Next time...
I'll ask to kiss you, first.
Please tell me how
you feel, then.
If you don't want this,
I promise to respect
your boundaries.
Shirayuki. Did you hear me?
[ZEN]
Well, we should head back.
It's about to get dark, so
we should probably hurry.
[BRECKER]
This is all absurd.
A girl without any social
status whatsoever has no place
in the court of a prince.
It's treachery.
[MITSUHIDE]
Kiki. What now?
I'm thinking a trip
to the island.
[KIKI]
Mm.
[ZEN]
Ready? Let's move out.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[OBI]
Uh!
Her hands. They're hot.
[SHIRAYUKI] I had heard Zen
say my name so many times.
But now there was a
warmth in his voice,
a flame in a color I'd
never seen before.
[OBI yawns]
[KIHAL] Shirayuki,
I don't know what to do!
I can't believe
the prince himself
is escorting me back
to the island!
I don't understand what
you're so nervous about.
Uh, we're talking about
His Royal Highness!
[ZEN]
Kihal! Sorry to make you wait!
Are you ready to go home?
Yes, I am, Your Highness!
The fastest route
to Yuris Island
is to follow this mountain pass.
We'll emerge right at the coast.
And from there, it's a
short journey by sea.
[SHIRAYUKI] Be calm.
Just keep breathing.
No one's gonna notice
anything's weird.
[KIHAL] Right. We should get
there in no time at all.
[gasps]
Shirayuki. Did you
come to see Kihal off?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh! Uh-huh. Yes.
I did, yes.
[ZEN]
How's your arm doing?
[SHIRAYUKI] Oh, better, thanks.
Ryu's keeping an eye on it.
[ZEN]
I'm glad to hear that.
You know what's wrong with her?
Shirayuki's been acting weird
ever since we finished
the bird test.
Yeah, you're right.
And Zen seems normal,
which is even stranger.
I thought that was
kinda weird, too!
No doubt it's because something
happened between them.
[BOTH]
What?! What do you mean?
Take a guess...
[ZEN] Hey, what are you
all waiting for? Let's go.
Uh! Right!
[OBI]
Too bad.
It would've been nice if I
could've gone with them.
But I guess somebody's
gotta watch over you.
Tell me something.
When you and the prince
were alone together
that day in the watchtower...
Did he give you a hard time?
[SHIRAYUKI] Hm? No,
of course he didn't!
[OBI]
Hm. My mistake.
I'm gonna figure out
what happened, though.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Well, I'm running late,
so I'd better head
over to work, now!
Uh. Wait. Hey!
She'll never tell me anything.
[SHIRAYUKI pants]
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
It's been three days
since we kissed,
so why am I still such a mess?
Every time he comes near me I
get flustered all over again.
[ZEN] Please tell me
how you feel, then.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Nothing like this
has ever happened
between us before.
It's new.
How can I tell him
how I feel when
I can't even figure
it out for myself?
[GRANDFATHER]
You want to use the birds
as a means of communication?
[MITSUHIDE
Yes.
Kihal helped us
to test the idea,
and the results were
highly successful.
We believe this system
could be implemented
throughout the entire kingdom.
That said, it's important
to protect the birds,
so we will need
your cooperation.
We'd like to bring a few of
your people to the castle
to help train the soldiers to
handle the animals properly.
That way none would be harmed.
[ISLANDER A]
Is he serious?
[MALE ISLANDER B]
I think so.
[MITSUHIDE] We understand
there has been some conflict
with poachers,
but this proposition
could quite possibly put
an end to that permanently.
[GRANDFATHER] In order to trust
that your motives are sincere,
I have two requests.
We want a formal apology
from Lord Brecker,
and a consolation payment.
I think ten million dil
would be appropriate.
Ten million?!
[MITSUHIDE] Paying you
isn't the best way to prove
that we're sincere
in our requests.
[ZEN] Hm. I'll do my very
best to get a formal apology
from the Viscount,
but the money's a different
matter. Your thoughts, Kiki?
Let me consider. Ten million
dil is a lot of money.
What if we offered you
twenty million instead?
Would you agree to
the terms then?
[gasps]
If we used money and power to
bribe you into acceptance,
we'd be as bad Brecker.
Paying you isn't the
best way to prove
that we are sincere
in our requests.
[ISLANDERS gasp]
[GRANDFATHER] Forgive me
for speaking disrespectfully,
Your Highness. We would
be honored to cooperate.
Great. I look forward
to working with you.
[BOYS cheer]
[BOY A] Um, Prince Zen?
Are you real royalty?
Hey! Leave him alone!
Yep! I sure am.
[BOYS sigh]
Oh, wow! A true blue
prince, no way!
So, Prince! What's it like
to live in a castle?
Do you wanna try some
of our food maybe?
[BOYS chattering]
All right, kids.
You can have an audience
with the prince one at a time.
[BOYS]
Wow!
[BOYS chattering, laughing]
It's like they forgot I exist.
[GRANDFATHER] That young man
saw through me immediately,
didn't he? I couldn't
believe my ears.
I assumed a prince must
be as bad as the viscount.
And I suppose I was wrong
to make such a blind
assumption about him.
[MITSUHIDE] Getting some
fresh air, Highness?
[MITSUHIDE]
Will you permit me to join you?
[ZEN] Only if you
stop talking like that.
Thank goodness.
[ZEN]
Where's Kiki?
[MITSUHIDE] She thought I
should be the one to do this.
The one to do what?
[MITSUHIDE]
To find out what happened
between you and Shirayuki.
[gasps]
What's going on?
[ZEN sighs]
I kissed her.
In the watchtower.
[MITSUHIDE]
Huh.
What?! You've gotta
be kidding me!
Are you sure you didn't
dream it or something?
I know what's real life!
Uh. So, then,
how did she react?
[ZEN]
Uh... It's hard to say.
She got quieter than
I've ever seen her.
[MITSUHIDE]
Really? Did she say anything?
[ZEN] No, she looked
shocked and turned red.
So she blushed?!
She did! Stop acting
like I'm making this up!
[MITSUHIDE]
I just can't believe it. Heh.
[ZEN] I've felt like this about
Shirayuki for a long time.
Maybe even since
the day we first met.
When I kissed her,
it was undeniable.
It took me over.
Now, I want to tell her how
I feel, but I can't yet.
[MITSUHIDE] Zen, she doesn't
care what you are.
[ZEN]
Hm?
[MITSUHIDE]
Never mind.
[ZEN grunts]
What did you mean by that?
Hell, I don't care
who you are, either.
None of us serve you
because you're a prince.
We couldn't care less.
[ZEN]
I know.
[SHIRAYUKI] I finished
cooking the riko fruit.
[RYU]
Great, grind it up.
I'm almost done weighing
out the rudro leaves.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Sure!
[OBI] What are the two of
you doing with all that?
Hm?
[SHIRAYUKI]
We're making a medicinal tea.
The Chief has pulled a few
all-nighters in a row,
and she's at her breaking point.
Which means she's
less than agreeable.
[RYU] If we make her
a restorative drink,
she should be nice enough for
us to make it through the day.
[OBI] Does she need medicine?
Why not a pot of regular tea?
[SHIRAYUKI] Because we
sorta wanted to experiment
with herbs on her.
It's done!
This is gross.
What if we added sugar,
and maybe some julia flowers?
It would taste better,
but make it less potent.
What do we have that's more
like the other ingredients?
[OBI]
Roka fruit?
It tastes pretty sweet,
and may add to the effect.
I've never tried boiling
roka in water before.
[ALL slurping]
[laughs]
[GARAK groans]
[GARAK]
I have so much work to do.
Did you get any sleep?
We made this for you.
It's roka tea. Drink up!
You did what?
[sniffs]
Smells good.
Tastes great!
[SHIRAYUKI laughs]
[sighs] You know, this would
be the perfect thing
to add to kids'
medicine for flavor.
The sweet notes
will cut bitterness,
but it won't
decrease the effect!
Uh. Interesting.
I never imagined
children wouldn't like
the taste of medicine.
I'm pretty impressed
that you two had the idea
to make me roka tea.
Oh, Obi should get the credit.
[OBI]
Mm? Uh?!
Really?
Well, you did learn about
roka fruit first hand
that day you helped
us harvest it.
Uh. It was nothing really,
just a little beginner's luck.
I think it was a bit
more than that.
This idea came about when you
put your heads together.
Your different perspectives
seem to spark your creativity.
Sounds like you all
make the perfect team.
That's good to know
for the future.
Shirayuki. After you finish
that you can call it a day.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What? You don't need me?
[RYU] We're already
way ahead thanks to you.
Oh, but, I don't mind.
I could use something to
keep me busy, so, I can stay.
I want to stay.
[RYU]
What do you mean?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh, well... Uh. It's nothing.
[RYU]
It's something.
And if it worries you,
then try writing about it.
[OBI, GARAK]
Uh?
It might make you feel better.
[bell tolls]
[SHIRAYUKI] Ryu's even
worried about me, now.
He's right, though.
I can't just keep
distracting myself
from thinking about that kiss.
I should take some time
to really figure out
how I feel about Zen.
[SHIRAYUKI]
The forest.
[OBI]
Uh. You wanna go?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes, if that's all right.
[OBI] Unless they're
using it for training,
we should be able
to go in, no problem.
Let's do it.
[OBI] Even though the forest
is on castle grounds,
it's still a bit of a hike.
[OBI]
She's not even talking anymore.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki!
Oh, hello, there, Master!
You're back so early!
[ZEN]
Not true, we're right on time.
Where are you two going?
We had trouble finding you.
Shirayuki?
What's the matter with you?
What are you hiding for?
I... I'm not ready, yet.
I can't face him.
What?
Fine! Run away, now, Miss!
Uh...
What?
Go, run into the forest!
You've got a head start!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
She ran away.
[OBI laughs]
Weird, why would she do that?
Because you told her to!
[OBI] I don't know what you're
talking about. What'd I do?
It's not like I'm the one
she's running from, is it?
[ZEN] Mitsuhide, Kiki, Obi.
I'm going after her.
Wait at the castle.
[BOTH]
Yes, sir. As you wish.
[OBI] Don't worry, Miss.
He's on his way.
[SHIRAYUKI panting]
[SHIRAYUKI]
What did I run away for?
What if he follows me out here?
I don't think I've ever felt
this stupid in my life.
[ZEN] Shirayuki!
What is the matter with you?
[SHIRAYUKI] Nothing! I just
can't face you right now.
I don't know what to say.
[ZEN]
Will you please stop running?
This is getting a
little ridiculous.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You have nothing
to feel bad about.
If the tables were turned,
I'd be running, for sure.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh? It's not about the kiss.
I was surprised, but
there's more to it.
So, what is it, then?
Was it the part where I asked
you to tell me how you felt?
[gasps]
[ZEN] The first time we met was
in a forest like this, remember?
Wanna stay? We can just
talk for a little while.
[ZEN]
Oh, right.
The meeting with the people
of Yuris Island went very well.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Really? That's wonderful.
[ZEN] We're moving forward
with the birds.
The next step is to build
the training squad,
so Kihal will be coming
back to the castle soon.
The wind feels better here than
anywhere else in the kingdom.
[birds chirping]
[SHIRAYUKI] Do you spend a
lot of time in the forest?
[ZEN] Mm... I used to,
just to get away from it all,
but then I started to practice
horseback riding out here.
That's when it stopped being
a relaxing place for me.
It's been a while.
I guess I prefer the forest
outside the grounds now.
I see.
Though having you with me
makes it lovely again.
You do change things.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[wind blows]
I love that sound.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Me, too.
[SHIRAYUKI] It was then
I started to realize,
since I met Zen,
things had changed.
The comfort and peace
I felt being around him
was growing into something new.
Something I'd never felt before.
Something I couldn't deny
to myself any longer.
[SHIRAYUKI cries]
[ZEN]
Hm?!
[SHIRAYUKI] Zen. I think
I'm in love with you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I've always cared about you
and had so much respect
for the person you are.
I thought I just wanted
to be there for you.
But, now, I know it's more
than being your friend...
And...
It scares me.
[SHIRAYUKI] I can't act
like things are the same
as they've been between us.
This is so much bigger than
anything I've ever felt before.
It almost hurts, and I don't
know what to do with it.
[SHIRAYUKI cries]
[ZEN] You're right.
It's different now.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki.
My title might not always
be able to protect you.
In fact, it might make life
harder for us sometimes.
The truth is,
situations will arise
where I'm forced to
choose my duty over you.
It's inevitable,
and I need you to understand
that in the beginning.
I don't care that it
may not be easy, though.
Together, we can
weather the storms.
You give me that faith.
I swear I will protect you and
what we have with my life.
It may seem strange, but
I'll need your help, too.
You inspire me like
no one I've met.
You are my strength.
I think you're my destiny.
So tell me.
If I reach out my hand,
Shirayuki, will you take it?
Yes. I'll take your hand, Zen.
[ZEN] There's something that's
plagued me for years now.
[ZEN]
Ever since I realized my title
could get in the way
of normal relationships,
I've been occupied
with a specific fear.
[ZEN]
Hey, Mitsuhide.
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes?
[ZEN]
Tell me honestly.
If I fell in love,
and decided that I wanted
to be with that person.
When they tell me
how they feel,
how will I know if they
love me for who I am?
Can I trust that people
won't love me for my title?
That they're not just
afraid to disobey me?
Will I ever be able
to believe them?
I'm afraid I'll never be
able to accept real love.
That my doubts will
always get in the way.
Will I ever not worry?
Shirayuki. Thank you.
[SHIRAYUKI] That voice
I'd heard so many times
sounded warm and new.
It lit a fire in my heart.
[ZEN]
Her eyes sparkled so tenderly.
They lit a fire in my heart.
[ZEN]
I will never forget this day.
[SHIRAYUKI]
When I look back on this moment,
I'll remember the
warmth of our kiss.
[ZEN]
I'll know that I'm loved.
[ZEN, SHIRAYUKI]
And that will give me courage.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Open Castle Day?
[MITSUHIDE]
Zen!
[SHIRAYUKI] I'm... not very
good at stuff like this.
[MITSUHIDE]
That's really great news.
Because we want
that for you, too.
[TROUPE LEADER]
Okay, wait for it.
This is the high
point of the show!