[ZEN] There's a messenger
coming from Tanbarun?
[IZANA] Arriving tomorrow.
From what I understand,
it's about what transpired
after Shirayuki's invitation.
Did she manage to make friends
with that foolish
prince of theirs?
[ZEN]
Well, I'd say either way,
Shirayuki does not think
of Raj as foolish.
[IZANA]
That's good to hear.
The girl gets along well
with princes, doesn't she?
[ZEN]
If that's how you feel,
why not build a better
relationship with her yourself?
[IZANA] No. If I became
friends with her,
you would just end
up being jealous.
Your concern is needless.
So you say, but I'll
hold back just in case.
Moving on.
If Tanbarun still has
need of Shirayuki,
I can't wait to find out why.
[ZEN] I shall go out to meet
the messenger, if you like.
[IZANA]
Sure.
[exhales]
[SHIRAYUKI]
That's the last of those.
All that's left
is pulling out these
weeds here in the front.
Oh, I still have to see how
the akime herbs are sprouting!
[footsteps]
[MAN yelps]
[MAN]
Obi! Get off of me!
Well, well, so I guess
it was you after all.
Hey, what do you
mean "after all"?!
Mihaya?
[MIHAYA]
Yes, that's right.
Just perfect. [exhales]
I'm here as an official
messenger from Tanbarun.
You should know that I went
out of my way to come see you
right after greeting
Prince Zen and the others.
If that's the case, then why
were you sneaking around
and hiding in the
shadows like a rat?
Because someone I
didn't want to see
was probably with her,
stray cat face!
Official messenger?
I didn't realize you
were in Tanbarun now.
That all happened when
you were kidnapped
by the Claw of the Sea.
Don't you remember I gave
them very important intel
so Tanbarun could
take them down?
Thanks to me, the thugs
associated with the Claw
were dragged out one by one,
and as a reward...
I was given a noble rank!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MIHAYA] It's not like
I have any power, but...
I don't care, 'cause
I'm the head of the
Sisk viscount family.
Wow. Seems like you've
been pretty active there.
Is that why you're here
as Tanbarun's messenger?
[MIHAYA]
No, I lied a bit.
I was just allowed to come
along since I know you.
The real official messenger
is someone else.
He has business
with you, Miss Red.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Why with me?
[footsteps]
[MITSUHIDE]
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'm so sorry I'm late!
Zen is inside. Prince Izana
is with him, as well.
That makes sense.
What's with the
messenger from Tanbarun?
Did something happen
to Prince Raj?
I don't think that's
the case, personally.
Well, I can't say I disagree.
Your Highnesses!
Miss Shirayuki has arrived.
Please, excuse me.
[SAKAKI]
Shirayuki, long time no see.
[gasps] Sakaki?!
[IZANA] Apparently, he
has something important
he wants to give you.
Prince Izana.
[IZANA] Zen and I thought it
would be best to have witnesses,
so we insisted upon
being present.
I come as a representative
of the prince of Tanbarun.
Shirayuki...
This is for you.
Prince Raj's message
is as follows:
"Tanbarun presents the title
'Friend of the Crown'
to Shirayuki of Clarines."
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
The title?
The redheaded girl
you've taken is special!
In Tanbarun, she is
held in high regard.
The only person to hold the
title "Friend of the Crown"!
Uh. No. That was a bluff.
I thought the title thing
was just part of the plan.
Yes, and based on that,
Prince Raj proposed it.
The king approved without much
hesitation, so here we are.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What?
With this, you'll now
be a state guest.
Prince Raj's goal was to
ensure you were allowed
to come to our kingdom
whenever you wished.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh. Uh...
Yes. Thank you very much.
Shirayuki.
Zen.
[IZANA laughs]
[ZEN, SHIRAYUKI]
He's laughing?!
Um. Are you all right?
Prince Izana?
[IZANA]
"Friend of the Crown", huh?
It's a bizarre title, for sure.
And yet... Nice.
Sorry, I'm not making fun.
This just caught me off guard.
[IZANA sighs]
[IZANA]
Previously...
I told Shirayuki that
being by Zen's side
would make him
appear incompetent.
At the very least, he'd
be a negligent prince.
[gasps]
[IZANA]
But now, with this title,
you two can call each other
friend with no worry.
[IZANA]
Shirayuki,
how would you like things
to be between you and Zen?
I don't believe I've ever
heard you speak of it before.
[gasps]
Although, to be honest,
what could you really say?
Congratulations on
your title, dear.
[door closes]
[SHIRAYUKI]
What could I say...?
[ZEN]
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Uh, oh sorry...
I'm all right.
I was just surprised.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki.
You don't have to
answer him now.
You don't even have
to think about it.
[RYU]
Just about done. You think so?
Yes.
[knocking]
[GARAK]
Hello, I'm coming in.
Ah-ha! There you are.
Please, go ahead, Sir.
Oh, Sakaki.
[GARAK] He said he wanted to
talk to you for a minute.
Well. Do you want to help
me with something, Ryu?
[RYU]
Right.
I apologize.
I interrupted your work.
No, it's fine.
We actually just reached
a perfect stopping point.
So...?
I still think of you as a
possible match for Prince Raj.
You're a good influence on him.
[gasps]
And I'd like to see
that continue.
Well, Prince Raj does not
seem to be interested,
but thank you nonetheless.
[SAKAKI]
That's a different story.
If I keep pushing,
the prince might break.
[SHIRAYUKI] It was my
understanding that Prince Raj
was motivated by
his own will, now.
Is he?
Although, if I were to guess,
he's probably sleeping
soundly right now.
[snoring]
[sneezes]
[yawns]
[SHIRAYUKI] Sakaki, how long
have you been with the prince?
Since he was five.
I was only 16 when I
started serving him.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Longer than I thought.
Well, I've mainly just
stood behind him.
But, that's why I have
been in an ideal position
to see things from his view.
The view with you
in it, by the way,
shone far brighter than most.
[gasps]
Not to mention how many
firsts that it involved.
I didn't realize.
The Prince entrusted me
with this. For you.
It's a personal letter.
To his very first friend.
[RAJ] "Shirayuki, I sincerely
hope you have been well.
My days have been hectic
as I move forward.
I sent Sakaki to Clarines
with your title,
and I am sure he has
been talking about
bringing you to me, but you
do not have to listen to him."
[RAJ]
"I feel like the current state
of our relationship
is perfectly fine.
The next comment might not
be any of my business,
but I shall write
it just in case.
About that title...
I realize it is not much
considering you already
have strong ties to royalty.
However, I am giving it to
you so it can be a shield.
You should hold onto
whatever you can
if there is nothing to
lose by having it...
I promise to do the same.
Yours, Raj Schenazade"
[SHIRAYUKI]
I will.
[OBI yawns]
[OBI] Who knew this would be
the most comfortable spot?
[yawns]
Huh?
[OBI]
Hello, Miss!
[gasps] Ah!
Obi. What are you doing?
Oh, you know me. Living
the nocturnal life.
I was wondering that
about you, Miss.
So what are you doing
out here before dawn?
I couldn't sleep...
I figured I'd go to
the herb garden.
[OBI] I've never seen
that expression before.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm!
[OBI laughs]
[OBI] I heard you received
a title from your homeland.
I expected you to be happier
about it, though.
[SHIRAYUKI] I am happy;
I'm just still in shock.
Prince Raj seems well.
Does he? Good. I guess
that's good to hear.
So, yesterday--
[OBI]
Something happened?
Not really. Just a lot
of thinking, I guess.
I don't know about
where I am, now.
About where you are, now?
I'm not sure if I get it.
Are you saying this
because you know about
where you do want to be?
[SHIRAYUKI]
No. I don't know at all.
Well, before you start making
everything too complicated,
I'm thinking you should
go talk to the master.
[SHIRAYUKI]
You're right.
Zen probably already thought it
through for me a long time ago.
[MITSUHIDE]
Really consider it.
And decide if the place
where Zen will take you...
...is also a place
where you wish to be.
[SHIRAYUKI]
About what lies ahead.
I can't... I don't know.
Going somewhere?
Obi. Will you please
help me get to him?
[OBI] Heh. I'm pretty
sure I already told you
that I would take you
wherever you wanted to go.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi!
[OBI] But this time, I think
I'll bring him to you.
Let me take care of it.
That's my job.
Wait here, Miss.
[footsteps, panting]
[footsteps]
[gasps]
[panting] Shirayuki!
Zen!
Shirayuki.
[gasps]
I, um...
I still haven't been able
to figure out a response
to Prince Izana's
question yesterday.
I'm so sorry for not
saying anything.
It just... It made
me realize that...
since the day I told
you that I loved you,
I haven't really said
much else about it.
I want you to know,
every single thing I
said then is still true.
[ZEN]
Good. I feel the same way.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
Is this realistic, or
am I fooling myself?
I love you so much.
I want to be by
your side someday.
But can I stand
next to a prince?
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Remember, you don't have
to think about this now.
Thank you.
Listen. I'm sorry.
I should tell you
something now.
Uh! Shirayuki?!
Oh. Sorry about that.
My legs just abandoned me.
[ZEN] Don't apologize.
This is my fault.
Do you, um... Do you
think you can stand?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Not with confidence.
[ZEN]
All right!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Let's go.
It's still too early for you
to have to work, right?
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh! Uh. What...?
Why is Obi sleeping
in Zen's room?
Well, hello there, Mitsuhide.
Did you sneak in here
for a lover's tryst?
No, but I certainly would like
to know what you're doing.
I've memorized everyone's
movements in this castle,
so don't worry!
Right, you had to
know to sneak out!
It's a lifelong habit, okay?
Don't try to change me.
[KAI]
I knew she was amazing!
She's the best, isn't she?
Will you keep it down?
And please find a
different topic;
you've been chattering
about this since yesterday.
But sir, she's a
Friend of the Crown!
It's a huge deal! Oh,
that's my Shirayuki.
[SHILA] You better not let
Prince Zen hear you say that!
[KAI]
Don't worry. I'll be fine!
Prince Zen is very generous!
[footsteps]
Uh?
[KIKI]
What are you two lurkers doing?
Lurking.
I got a report from the guards
that they had spotted Zen...
Since it's still dark,
I thought I'd check on him.
[OBI] And apparently, he
was meeting with Shirayuki.
I assume you knew about this.
Of course, I knew about it, but
I didn't know what it was about.
I'm sure he'll be back
before breakfast.
Yes. I agree.
You're not going to talk to him?
[MITSUHIDE]
Sometimes, an attendant's job
is to watch silently
from a distance.
As long as Zen
doesn't find out.
[ZEN panting]
[gasps]
Wow, the air is so fresh.
No one will bother
us in this place.
We're all alone.
Wait, I brought you here
because you couldn't stand!
And I didn't think you'd want
anyone to see you that way.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh! I can stand, now.
Thank you, though!
[ZEN]
Shirayuki, you should know,
I already told my
brother that I...
That I have feelings for you.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[ZEN]
And that's why...
No, not why, but it's about
what you said earlier.
[SHIRAYUKI] Is this realistic,
or am I fooling myself?
I want to be by
your side someday.
But can I stand
next to a prince?
I love you so much.
[ZEN] The answer to your
question is simple.
You can. Yes.
[ZEN]
It always has been yes.
I realize I'm being
selfish by asking this,
but please, wait.
I will use the proper
words one day.
I promise you that.
[SHIRAYUKI]
All right.
A promise to promise
is silly, huh?
Doesn't make me feel too clever.
No, it's fine.
And you are clever.
You amaze me every day.
You amaze me, too.
[door opens]
[ZEN]
Lord Brother!
Yes, what is it?
I'll see the Tanbarun
messengers off.
They're leaving at two.
Sounds good.
[ZEN]
That is all. Excuse me.
[door closes]
That was the first
time in his life
he did not avert
his eyes even once.
Raj appears to have become
very dependable, Sakaki.
I'm glad for him.
Thank you. He's coming along.
You're hard on poor Raj.
Yes, I know.
Until next time.
[gasps] Sakaki, wait!
Yes?
[SHIRAYUKI] This is my reply
to the letter Price Raj sent.
Will you give it to him for me?
Of course I will. I'll also
try to win you over again.
Next time I have the chance.
[SHIRAYUKI gasping]
Goodbye, dear Friend
of the Tanbarun Crown.
I do hope you'll be
friends with me, as well.
And if you need noble rank,
I don't mind adopting
you into my family.
Wha...?!
Next time he has
the chance. Really?
Oh, I'm sure he will.
Shirayuki has all sorts
of connections now.
Don't tell me,
he asked you to go back
to Tanbarun again?
Uh! Yes, you guessed correctly.
You know what, I don't
like the sound of that,
at all.
[laughs]
Wow. I really didn't
expect you to laugh...
All right. Shall we all
get back to work?
--[MITSUHIDE, KIKI] Yes, Sir!
--[OBI] Why not?
[MITSUHIDE]
We have an inspection schedule
meeting in the evening.
[KIKI] But you have reports you
need to look over before that.
[ZEN]
All right.
So then... See you later?
Of course.
Yes.
[SHIRAYUKI]
This is my own path.
My own story...
And I'm loving it.
Oh. So you're back with us?
I suppose you finished
seeing them off?
[SHIRAYUKI] Yes. Are you headed
to the dispensary now?
[RYU]
Yes, I thought I'd go ahead
and grind the stored
montlet herb we have.
Needs to be done while
it's still good.
I can go with you!
Appreciated.
[SHIRAYUKI]
If I could,
I would like to be able
to draw my own path
in whatever shape I want.
And, then...
I'd wish for that path to be
painted with the color of fate.
And that would be my story.