[IZANA]
All of these are requests
for marriage
interviews with Zen?
Yes. Here is list of candidates
brought up by the retainers,
as well, Your Highness.
I just can't believe
how many there are.
Was he passing out bouquets
on his way back from Tanbarun,
because this is ridiculous.
[HARUKA] Of course, half of the
reason is likely due to the fact
that you have not held any
marriage interviews
for him yet, Highness.
Zen is of age,
so his place in line for the
throne now holds more weight
to those clamoring
for a better position.
Power has a way of motivating.
It's unusual for you
to defend your brother from
his duty, Your Highness.
[IZANA]
That's not true.
I've always been this soft
on my brother, haven't I?
I've had fun talking
to him recently, too.
[HARUKA] If you would like,
I shall inform Prince Zen
that we need to hold a marriage
interview immediately.
[IZANA]
All right.
[bell tolls]
[SOLDIER A]
Prince Zen Wisteria
has finally returned
to the castle!
[IZANA grunting]
Good to see you, Lord Brother.
We've returned.
Welcome home, Zen.
I'm glad you're all safe.
I wonder, what will you do now?
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Hello, Chief Garak.
I've returned from Tanbarun.
I can work with you again.
Starting right now, in fact.
Long time no see, Shirayuki.
Welcome back.
[GARAK] Have you told
Prince Izana that you're here?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I have.
He said that I had
done "good work"
and that he would like to hear
more about it at a later date.
[GARAK]
Great.
Since you've had a long journey,
you should have a
lighter workload.
At least, that's what
I'd like to say,
but we just don't
have that luxury.
It certainly looks that way.
[crash]
[GARAK]
Uh?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ryu!
Oh, no!
No, she's not a ghost.
Our girl's come home.
Shirayuki.
Uh! Oh, sorry!
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's fine.
I don't think I've
ever seen this.
Is it for a new medicine?
[RYU] Yes. I thought
of it the other day.
Oh... So infuse the
tartsugi herb with it.
You don't mind if I try
that later on, do you?
[RYU] No. Let me know
when you do it, though.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Definitely.
Uh. Oh yeah, how did
the painkiller turn out?
[RYU]
It worked well.
I'll teach you the trick,
if you wanna come help me.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes! I would love to!
Of course they're talking
herbs immediately
after seeing each other,
they're nothing if not reliable.
She's done so well.
I'm not sure how much longer
this apprenticeship should last.
So do you think she's
ready for a final test?
I'll have to discuss
it with Ryu, first.
You did it.
The bitterness is reduced!
[RYU] I just had to adjust
the boiling temperature.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I see.
Oh. Looking for koko herb?
[RYU]
Oh, yeah. Shirayuki?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
[RYU]
Welcome back.
Ryu. It's great to be back.
Thank you!
[gassps] Hello there, Miss Kiki.
How are you today?
What are you doing
out here, Obi?
[OBI]
Heh. Truth be told,
a terrifying man came
to visit the master,
so I decided to run away.
Lord Haruka is talking
to Zen right now?
You figured that out fast.
Hey, so, Miss Kiki, d'ya
wanna go for a walk with me?
I don't.
[OBI] Mm. Then how else are
you gonna keep me company?
[HARUKA] Prince Izana has
also looked this over.
He said we could invite
them to the castle
and take care of
this all at once.
Are you listening,
Your Highness?
[ZEN] Of course I am.
I just won't do it.
[HARUKA]
Highness, please!
[OBI] They want to have a ball
to find a wife for the master?
[KIKI] Zen's gone to one
before meant for Prince Izana
to meet potential brides, but
he's never had one for himself.
[OBI]
Ah...
Well, this is unexpected.
Just what are you two doing?
Working.
[OBI]
Not me. I'm eavesdropping.
Please think about this
carefully, Highness.
This country needs your support,
as does your brother,
our next king.
[ZEN] I understand
my responsibilities,
and I will do what
is truly necessary.
That being said...
I have no intention
of finding a wife.
[HARUKA grunts]
Prince Zen.
[door opens]
[MITSUHIDE]
Excuse me, Your Highness.
Oh, good day, Lord Haruka.
[sighs] In any case,
doing nothing is not
presently an option for you.
[ZEN] I will not have
a ball, regardless.
Why would I if I'm not
looking for a wife?
No one's going to force
you to hold a ball.
However, you must, at least,
meet with one of
these candidates.
You need to demonstrate
that you have not completely
abandoned the idea of marriage.
You understand, don't you?
A one on one marriage
interview is even worse.
Uh?!
Now, every girl whose name is
on this list is a candidate.
Is that correct?
Of course,
I wouldn't necessarily
consider them equal, though.
You said I just had to meet
with one of them, right?
[KAI] Have you heard,
Sir?! This is terrible!
Why, because you have to
pay a fine? You're late.
No, that's not it!
Prince Zen is having a
marriage interview today!
Uh! The prince is looking
for a wife? Who is it with?
[KAI]
That's being kept a secret.
I thought for sure the prince
would get engaged to Shirayuki.
[SHILA] Wow, you really do
like that girl, don't you?
[KAI]
Mm-hm. [cries]
[SHILA] Aw, stop crying! I won't
make you pay a fine, okay?
[KAI cries]
Thank you, Sir.
You what? Seriously? Oh, my.
Yeah.
I overheard some servants
gossiping about it earlier.
[GARAK] Goodness. Prince Zen's
having a marriage interview.
I wonder if Shirayuki
knows about this?
I don't know.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Excuse me.
[GARAK gasping]
I finished inventory, and we
look good, just a bit short.
We need shiklas seeds
and koko herb.
But, other than those,
we're completely stocked up.
Um. Right, that's great to hear.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I think next
I'll go check the medicinal
shelves' inventory.
Sure. Sounds good.
Wait, isn't that what you
just finished doing, though?
Uh. Right, I guess
it is. I, um...
How about the deliveries?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
Shirayuki, shall I go instead?
No, no. I can take care of it.
I'm fine.
Excuse me.
I dunno. She doesn't
seem that fine to me.
[RYU]
Mm.
[SHIRAYUKI inahles, exhales]
This way, if you please.
Of course, Your Highness.
[MITSUHIDE]
Even if it's under the pretense
of a marriage interview,
I never thought
I'd witness this.
So strange.
Master said he's never been
more scared of her reaction
than when he asked for this.
Heh. That was hilarious.
Maybe for you,
but I was terrified.
So this is a farce?
It's not, mostly.
My brother has given
his permission,
so everyone else will think
the whole thing is legitimate.
Besides, if you play along,
you'll be helping me avoid
dealing with this situation
for a little while.
Oh, and in order to protect
your position as my attendant,
I have already received
a pledge to keep your name
from being made public.
I believe this is
our best option.
Unless you wanted me
to have a grand ball
that you'd have to attend?
[OBI laughing]
[OBI] I had no idea that
Miss Kiki's father was a count.
Talk about an
unexpected surprise.
"Daughter of a count" sounds
pretty good on her, doesn't it?
[MITSUHIDE]
I don't know.
Even though this
is just an act,
those two look good
together, don't they?
Indeed, they do.
[OBI]
Mitsuhide,
I know you're calm right now
because she's with the master.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh?!
But if it was another
man that close to her,
you wouldn't be back
here with me.
You'd be over there "defending
her honor" or something.
Don't assume you can get away
with teasing me like you do Zen.
See, your problem is
you have no imagination.
If Miss Kiki were to
speak of her intentions
with some man other than you,
that would mean they'd
be there for each other, and
she'd take his side over yours.
But, I am just teasing you.
I wonder...
[OBI] Oh, did the atmosphere
suddenly turn violent?
[MITSUHIDE sighs]
Listen, Obi.
Make sure you don't
joke around like this
about the marriage interview
with Shirayuki, all right?
[OBI]
Why not?
Wait, has no one let her know
what's really going on, yet?
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh!
Not as far as I
know, we haven't.
[OBI]
Then, I shall leave this to you.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh! [gasping]
Yes, you're welcome.
[sighs]
One more down.
After this, I think I
only have a few more--
[OBI]
Hello, Miss!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Obi!
Why are you dressed
up like that?
[OBI]
Well...
Oh, that's right,
the marriage interview
must have already started.
[OBI]
Uh...
[SHIRAYUKI] But, is it all
right for you to be here?
Yes, about that.
I'm not needed since things
are going so smoothly.
[SHIRAYUKI]
They're going smoothly?
Oh! No, wait.
By "smoothly" I mean it's
because the girl...
[ZEN]
I have already received a pledge
to keep your name
from being made public.
Uh-oh. I don't think I can say.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Hm?
She, uh...
Hey, wanna hear a joke?
[SHIRAYUKI] Later. I have some
work I have to finish, first.
Uh...
Not your finest moment, Obi.
[ZEN grunts]
You seem uncomfortable.
Not me. What about you?
I'm sorry.
I know you don't like wearing
dresses, even in the castle.
No, I don't. My sword
is farther away.
Don't worry though.
I still have a dagger on me.
Definitely marriage material.
Speaking of which,
you were wearing a dress the
first time you met Mitsuhide.
Do you remember that night?
Oh, yes. I certainly do.
It's been five years
already, huh?
I guess it has.
[KIKI]
What if I had just stayed home?
[LADY A] Sir Louen isn't in
attendance tonight, either?
He was here until
just a moment ago.
[sighs] I tried, but I just
don't like these things.
Uh!
Excuse me, Miss.
I didn't realize somebody
was already out here.
[KIKI] Don't apologize.
Mitsuhide Louen,
attendant of Prince Zen.
[MITSUHIDE]
Mm! You mean, you know who I am?
Do you mind if I
ask who you are?
Wait for the right moment.
Then, I'll tell you.
[MITSUHIDE gasping]
I don't like these things
as well, by the way.
Uh! You...
So you heard me?
Well, that's perfect.
Mitsuhide! Are you hiding
in a corner again?!
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Zen!
I see. I didn't realize
you two had met.
Uh?
If you'll excuse me.
D'you bring her out here?
[MITSUHIDE]
No!
It's dark...
[MITSUHIDE]
I said no!
Who was she, anyway?
[ZEN]
Didn't she tell you?
[MITSUHIDE] She said she
would at the right moment.
[ZEN]
Hm... It's a secret.
It is?! Why's is that?
Well, truth be told, I just
met her the other day.
I think you should
try talking to her
when that moment
is finally right.
What is it?
I don't know. Just seems
you really like her.
I do.
Then I'll be sure to ask
her for her name again.
Glad you're here.
And sorry I asked
for this match.
[KIKI]
It's fine.
By the way,
Mitsuhide said you wouldn't
tell him your name?
I wanted to meet him here,
with my sword in hand.
Makes sense to me.
--[door opens]
--[MITSUHIDE] Prince Zen!
[ZEN] Speak of the devil,
and he shall appear.
[MITSUHIDE] I thought you were
planning to rest this morning.
Oh, right. I changed my mind.
Why didn't you tell me?
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh?
We were just having a
little practice match.
Excuse me, but have we
met somewhere before?
[KIKI]
Mm?
[ZEN]
Huh?
I feel like we have. Uh! Sorry.
I just didn't realize
there was a noble boy here
this close to your
age, Prince Zen.
Shame I missed the match.
I would have liked
to've seen it.
I can't believe...
You are such a huge idiot.
[MITSUHIDE]
Hm?
[KIKI] Let's just call this
our first time meeting, then.
My name is Kiki.
Hello. It's a pleasure
to meet you.
[ZEN laughs]
He thought you were a boy
for a while, didn't he?
Indeed he did.
He kept calling me "noble boy"
and inviting me to the baths.
That guy. Look at him.
[MITSUHIDE]
Hm?
He's so dense I almost feel
guilty remembering that.
Though, I must say,
he hasn't really changed
much since then.
Still prioritizes
you over everyone.
Still wears his heart
on his sleeve,
and is still a bundle of nerves.
And yet, he sees things
that are simply beyond me.
Things I can't even imagine.
This is unusual.
You're not normally
so open with me.
Well, we have spent quite
a long time together
while keeping an eye
out for each other.
Got it.
For what it's worth, I'm glad
you two met each other.
[KIKI]
So, what's next?
Do you have any plans
for when the effect
of this marriage
interview wears off?
No, not yet,
but I couldn't've had a fake
interview with anyone better.
[ZEN]
The intent to take a wife?
Whoa. The marriage
interview is already over?
That was quicker
than I expected.
But it's done and I've
managed to stall some
before having to hold a
grand ball to find a wife.
I have another
concern, though.
How many times do I have
to tell you not to run off
while you're on duty?
Sounds like someone
else we know.
I told you, I made a
proper request this time.
Oh, no, what happened, Master?
I left and was gone from
the castle too long.
So, I can't leave for a while.
All I want to do is go talk
to Shirayuki. Especially, now.
I want to tell her the truth
about the marriage
interview in person.
Uh... About that, Master.
[ZEN]
Hm?
[crash]
You what...?
I need you to repeat that.
[OBI]
I just said,
Shirayuki actually already knows
about the marriage interview
thanks to all the gossipmongers
around the castle.
[ZEN]
After that!
You mean where I sort of
mentioned I didn't tell her
the girl was Miss Kiki.
That?
Yes, that.
If you were talking about
the marriage interview,
why did you leave out
the most important part?
Uh. Because we...
...were supposed to hide the
fact that it was Miss Kiki?
Yes, but not from Shirayuki!
So sorry.
Are you all right, Zen?
Listen. I have to go to her.
I'll pull an all-nighter
if you want me to.
Well, don't stay out too late!
What are the odds this guy's
gonna get punished later?
A sure thing.
[door opens]
[panting] Ryu, where is she?
[RYU] Shirayuki?
She's in the herb garden.
[ZEN]
Thank you!
[footsteps]
Finished.
All that's left is to plant
the rainbow leaf seedlings.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki!
Oh, Zen!
[panting]
[SHIRAYUKI]
What?!
You mean your marriage
interview was with Kiki?
[ZEN]
Yes.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I see.
[ZEN]
I just wanted you to know.
This was... was not... anything.
And I am so sorry.
I didn't plan on
keeping it from you.
No, it's all right.
It didn't bother me.
[ZEN]
Uh?
It didn't bother you for me
to have a marriage interview?
Uh? Uh...! Yes, no!
I didn't mean it like that!
It's not that I had
no feelings about it.
Like when I first heard, my
heart wouldn't stop pounding.
But I also figured
you'd come and tell me
what was going on, so...
[ZEN] You were waiting
for me to come to you?
Uh! No...
...maybe...
Not technically?
But, ah...
I suppose...
I wanted to go see you,
but I thought I should wait.
All right,
everything's all right.
[SHIRAYUKI] Zen, you know
I'm happy, don't you?
I'm really happy that
you're here right now,
and that you're with me.
[door opens]
[IZANA]
I'm coming in.
[ZEN]
Lord Brother.
[IZANA] I thought you'd
come to ask me for help,
but you managed that marriage
interview yourself.
Tell me,
are you going to have one
with Mitsuhide next time?
Well, I guess I'm the one
who didn't take Kiki's
name off the list.
I want a drink. Care to join me?
[IZANA]
I'm curious.
Were you studying that book you
had open at your desk earlier?
[ZEN gasps]
I was.
I wanted to learn a little
about the situation up north.
You mean the one that
is my responsibility?
Will you come save me
if I'm in trouble?
If the day you ask me
for help ever comes.
That would hardly be
my decision, though.
Saving me is up to you.
[gasps]
[IZANA] Zen, you need
to understand something.
I'm planning to take a wife
sooner than you may realize.
Once that happens,
you will be next.
You'll be given one marriage
proposal after another.
Every choice you make,
every position you'll
eventually have,
and of course, where I decide
you ultimately belong,
they are for our kingdom,
for our people who put
their faith in your future.
You are their Prince.
[ZEN] Someone who cannot
handle that responsibility
cannot be a prince, I assume.
But I still want her.
I want Shirayuki to be my wife.
I had a feeling it
would come to this.
You should know you're
wrong about her.
And having that girl in my life
is not going to divert
me from my path.
Then leave her behind.
[ZEN]
Lord Brother,
I have no intention of
leaving Shirayuki behind.
No matter what happens.
I understand.
[IZANA]
Lift up your face, Zen.
If that's the case,
then you should make
me an ally on the path
you and Shirayuki have chosen.
[ZEN gasps]
[MITSUHIDE]
The path ahead.
It will be difficult, because of
the fact that Zen is a prince.
[KIKI]
Your highness.
You still have a lot
to learn, don't you?
[MITSUHIDE] Shirayuki, I want
you to be sure of your decision.
[ZEN] I need her by my side.
She's the only one
I want to be with.