[footsteps]
[MIHAYA]
I wonder...
how is Red getting along?
Can't wait to find out.
[SHIRAYUKI yelping]
[crash]
Oh, Shirayuki!
Did you hurt yourself?
No, I'm fine.
[YATSUFUSA] You're making
so much progress, Chief.
I think you should
keep it up here.
Shirayuki and I should be able
to take care of the medical
wing by ourselves.
Is that right?
Well then...
Take this.
Just a few things
to keep in mind
when you're organizing
the herb shelves.
Don't let me down, Yatsufusa.
Wow, you certainly went into
a lot of detail with these.
I guess now it makes sense
why you seemed so happy
when I suggested we
could take it over.
"Regarding the
painkiller alisia.
Check condition and
move if necessary.
Split the fever-reducer
shimagaeshi
into raw and dried sections."
Well, I'm not gonna learn
unless I try this myself.
I'm off to organize those herbs!
[YATSUFUSA] I didn't realize
she knew where herb storage was.
Pretty impressive.
That's the first
thing she learned
when she started working here.
Nice. It's great to see her
so motivated to excel.
She's proving to be
an invaluable asset
around this place.
She's developed a good
master-apprentice relationship
with Ryu, too.
If you're not careful,
she'll wind up eclipsing
you, Yatsufusa.
I'd like to see her try.
That can't be right.
The record says when the
herbalist prescribed this,
it had a pungent scent,
but it smells sweet, now.
Uh! Looks like bugs have
been eating at the stem.
Hm?
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's blooming.
Uh!
[OBI]
Hm?
Hey, Half-Pint, whatcha doin'?
It's Obi.
[OBI]
Uh, oh. Probably want that, huh?
[RYU]
Mm-hm.
So uh, you gonna get it down?
I've never climbed
a tree before.
What?! Are you serious?!
[sighs] I can't
even imagine that.
Come on. You might as well try.
[OBI]
Already done?
[RYU grunting]
It's fine, don't be scared.
You're lucky I'm here
to lend a hand.
Upsy-daisy.
Can you reach it now?
[OBI] How old are you
again, Half-Pint?
[RYU]
Um, I'm 12.
[OBI] You weigh next to nothing!
Right, got it, then?
[RYU]
Yes, thank you.
[OBI]
Good job!
Want me to carry you to
the medical wing like this?
Uh. But they're cleaning up,
and I don't want
to be in the way--
[OBI laughs]
Why is Zen working so hard?
He snuck over to see
Shirayuki earlier
and she was really busy.
I guess he decided to
double his efforts.
He can't let her
beat him. Right?
Shirayuki's the best motivator
Zen has had in years, isn't she?
Yes, she is. But he's
still working too hard.
[ZEN yelps]
[MITSUHIDE, KIKI]
Mm?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just a minor paper cut.
[MITSUHIDE]
Still...
You should go to the medical
wing and let them see.
Don't be ridiculous.
Believe what you want, Zen,
but just so you know,
people have died because of
minor paper cuts like this.
Do you think I'm stupid?
[MITSUHIDE] The tiny fibers
enter the bloodstream
and quickly multiply,
until the victims transform
into monstrous paper people!
[ZEN]
Fine, I'll go,
just spare me the horror drama.
I'm sure I'll be back shortly.
Mm?
I'll walk with you.
I'm helping the soldiers with
their training this morning.
They asked me not to go
easy on them this time.
They'll regret that.
Have fun torturing them.
[KIKI]
Heh. You know I will.
Now you can visit her without
feeling guilty about it.
I know,
but going for such a small cut
will probably get me laughed at.
[KIKI] Shirayuki would
never make fun of you.
Very true.
She always seems to take me
seriously, no matter what.
That's why I can't do
anything halfway anymore.
The last thing I want is to
give her reason to laugh at me.
[gasps]
[ZEN]
Lord Brother.
You think he realizes
where we're headed?
I'm sure he does.
If that smirk is any clue,
he's the one laughing at me.
It's fine.
He won't have reason
to mock me for long.
I swear it.
Whoa, what's goin' on here?
[RYU] We're drying out all
the research instruments.
[OBI]
So that's why you were outside.
I get it now, Half-Pint.
Hey! I've never
seen that flower.
What does it treat?
Oh, that isn't a
medicinal plant.
Shirayuki put it there
for decoration.
[OBI]
Mm.
That's nice.
It's quite a lovely addition.
[RYU]
Uh.
[SHIRAYUKI groaning]
Come on, door!
Obi!
And Ryu!
[OBI] Should I just put this
anywhere I can find room for it?
Yeah. Thank you.
Your timing is perfect.
Ryu, here's the herb
inspection form.
[OBI] Are there more boxes?
I can help you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'm fine!
And having a lot of fun learning
about all the instruments
in there I haven't seen before.
[RYU] Shirayuki, what's this
note about the enel herb?
The smell seems to have changed
from the last time
it was prescribed.
It was pungent,
but smells sweet now.
Any sign of bugs?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Definitely.
Some mock enel must have
gotten mixed in, then.
I was sure I'd been
careful, though.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Should we get rid of it?
[RYU]
Mm.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I can take care of that.
I'm pretty sure there's
some in storage
that was collected
the other day.
I should probably check
on that batch, too.
[RYU]
Yes.
All right. I'm gonna
get back to work!
Oh.
Looks like cleaning the lab
is going to take longer
than we originally thought.
[door closes]
[OBI]
What a strange girl.
She's the only person I know
who could learn by cleaning.
She is learning a lot that way.
Do you think that because
of what she told you
about the enel stuff?
[RYU]
Yes.
[OBI]
Mm...
Well, see ya.
Oh. Hold on a sec.
[RYU]
Oh!
[OBI chuckles]
[OBI]
Hm?
These are seeds of
the orbia flower.
From my personal supply.
They're for you.
Are you serious?
Yes, for helping me
get the paper.
[ZEN]
Excuse me, Chief.
Prince Zen.
How may I help you?
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I've just got
a measly paper cut.
[HIGATA]
Uh!
You've caught us in the middle
of our semi-annual cleaning.
[ZEN]
I see.
If you're looking for Shirayuki,
she's in the storage area.
[ZEN grunts]
I can take a look at it, though.
Paper cuts are dangerous.
You wouldn't want to turn into
a paper person, would you?
Did Mitsuhide tell you
to say that?!
[GARAK]
Wouldn't you like to know?
Here, let's clean that up,
and then if you want you
can wait in the bunk room.
Thanks. I really appreciate it.
Next!
[YATSUFUSA] Chief Garak. We're
finally finished cleaning.
Oh, that's good
to hear. Nice job!
And thank you for
working so hard.
You're all done
for the day, guys.
Oh! Shirayuki, there's a
visitor waiting for you
in the bunk room.
What? A visitor?
Um, Zen...?
Must be tired.
[ZEN] Together, we can
weather the storms.
You give me that faith.
I swear I will protect you and
what we have with my life.
[gasps] He's hurt?
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI gasping]
I've been wanting
to talk with you
about what the future
holds for us.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh.
--[knocking]
--[gasps]
[MITSUHIDE]
Shirayuki, it's me, Mitsuhide.
May I come in?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh, yes!
[yawns]
[MITSUHIDE]
I suppose I should have known
why you didn't return sooner.
[ZEN] Sorry, I didn't realize
how exhausted I was.
Don't worry about it.
If you need to sleep a little
longer, I think you should.
[ZEN]
Right. Good idea.
Did you forget something?
Just wanted to see
your face again.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[ZEN]
See ya.
[SHIRAYUKI]
My heart...
I feel like it could beat
right out of my chest.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What the future holds for us.
[bell tolls]
[OBI humming]
[ZEN gasps]
Obi!
You shouldn't lounge around
in someone else's room!
As I recall,
my position here is messenger
to the second prince
of Clarines.
If the prince doesn't
give me any work,
it means I can do
what I want, right?
[OBI]
Uh?
Pretty. Did you get
this from Shirayuki?
[OBI]
Uh. No, it was a gift from Ryu.
You don't have any trouble
making friends with people, huh?
Except Kiki.
[laughs]
Uh.
[ZEN] I heard Shirayuki's
trying to collect those
in all the different
flowering colors.
The seeds don't indicate the
color of the petals, though,
so it's hard.
She wants as many
as she can get.
[OBI]
Huh.
[AIDE A]
Excuse me.
[door opens]
[AIDE A] Prince Izana,
I'm sorry to disturb you,
but we've just received
correspondence from Tanbarun.
Oh? Interesting.
[OBI]
Half-Pint.
[RYU]
Mm?
These seeds. Take 'em back.
What for?
I've never grown flowers
from seed like this,
and I don't know how much longer
I'm gonna be in the castle.
So I think you should take them
and grow them for yourself.
Well, I think all that means
it's better for you
to have them.
Uh. What do you mean?
Nothing.
The seeds are pretty
just as they are,
and when you plant them,
they grow without much effort.
So when you leave here and
get where you might stay,
you can just plant them there.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Ryu!
Oh, good, I was hoping that
I would find you here!
I didn't expect
to see you, Obi.
Surprise.
[SHIRAYUKI] Cleaning the lab
took longer than I thought,
and I couldn't find
you when I was done,
so I started to get worried.
But since you're with Obi,
there's no cause for concern.
[OBI gasps]
The flowers.
Did they all fall
off or something?
No. I finished collecting
all the seeds I needed,
so I pruned them.
That's removing the blooms.
It'll help the plant
live a lot longer.
I heard about your quest.
Have you found all the
different colors, yet?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Almost. I'm just missing blue.
[OBI]
Uh.
Oh, well.
I'll just have to wait
until next year.
I'd like to see them
when you've got them all.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm-hm.
Uh.
[MITSUHIDE]
Shirayuki!
[SHIRAYUKI]
What?! Mihaya?
[ZEN]
Yes. He wants to speak with us.
That is, you and
me, specifically.
But I'm sure you'd
rather not see him.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I can't disagree.
Wait. Is that the
former noble guy
who kidnapped Shirayuki
a while back?
He's a good-for-nothing
scoundrel!
[OBI] I've never seen Zen
react like this before.
Mihaya is an enemy.
What could he possibly
want with us?
And I thought he was in jail.
[ZEN]
From what I know,
he wants to discuss something
that involves you.
Well, that's odd.
What do you say?
I'll see him.
Hello.
It's been a while,
hasn't it, Rosylocks?
[yelps]
Dispense with the small talk
and tell us why the
hell you're here!
Well, this might seem
a little strange, Red.
I mean, Shirayuki, so sorry.
Do you know of a very pretty
boy with light brown hair
who's about 13 or 14?
[gasps]
A "pretty" boy, he says, a
"very pretty" one, at that.
[MIHAYA] Does that
description ring a bell?
What about the name Kazuki?
Kazuki?
Why don't you drop the games and
tell us what you're getting at!
[MIHAYA]
Yes, Majesty.
After I was released from jail,
I didn't have any money,
so I thought I would go try
to find a way to earn some.
Well, I ended up on a ship...
[CAPTAIN A]
Red hair?
Yes, a teenage girl that has
bright red hair, like an apple.
Ain't seen no one like that.
So, kid, you got a thing
for red heads or what?
[KAZUKI] Don't be vulgar!
And I'm not a kid!
[MIHAYA]
Hey, kid, over here!
I'm no kid, and
my name's Kazuki!
All right, Kazuki.
I've seen that red-haired
girl of yours.
[gasps]
You gave him information
about Shirayuki?
Yes. I told him a while
back I met a girl
lost in the mountains,
and that when I took her in,
someone from Wistal castle
came to claim her.
[SHIRAYUKI, ZEN]
Huh.
[MIHAYA]
Come on,
he would have found
out sooner or later
that you were here in the
castle, so no harm done.
There it is.
Now.
I'm not exactly asking for
anything for telling you this,
but a lot of money would be
nice, or if you can't do that,
I'd accept a position
in the castle.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
So, that's the real
reason you're here?!
[MITSUHIDE] Your highness!
Please, calm down!
Uh, if it helps at all,
I have information
I got from the kid to use
as a bargaining chip.
If you agree to my terms,
I promise to tell you
everything I know.
[ZEN growls]
Wait, hold on!
Uh...
Give it a moment.
[ZEN exhales]
I have no reason to trust you.
First, the information.
He explained why he was
looking for Shirayuki.
[KAZUKI]
What for? Heh.
There's a better place for
that girl than a castle.
She's a princess,
but not the kind that should be
kept hidden from the world.
What kind of place do ya mean?
It's been worth traveling
all the way to Clarines.
What does that mean?
[ZEN grunts]
Shirayuki,
did your red hair get you into
some kind of trouble again?
Like before, with the
Prince of Tanbarun?
[knocking]
[AIDE A]
Excuse me, Your Highness.
What is it?
[IZANA] Sorry to bother you.
I know it's rather late.
[ZEN] What business do you
have with me, Lord Brother?
[IZANA] Actually, I don't
have any business with you,
but I knew you'd be upset
if she came here alone.
[gasps]
Shirayuki, I've not
seen you in a while.
Yes. That's true, my lord.
[IZANA] It would appear that you
have been invited to a ball
in our neighboring
land of Tanbarun.
[BOTH gasp]
[IZANA] You do recall that we
hosted their first prince, Raj,
at Wistal Castle
not long ago, yes?
Their invitation is a
way of thanking you
for caring for him
during that visit.
Oh, Prince Raj.
[IZANA] I've heard that since
his return to Tanbarun,
Prince Raj has begun to
take his role as ruler
a lot more seriously.
Shirayuki.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm?
The advice you gave him must
have been good medicine.
Your words certainly seem to
have made quite the impact.
[gasps]
[IZANA] "If you want
me to respect you,
then rule my country like a
prince I can be proud of."
A request from someone
born in Tanbarun.
If my guess is right, Tanbarun
wants to have a look at the girl
who turned their prince around.
So that's your plan to
get rid of her, then?!
To give her over to Prince Raj?!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
If he's made such
great progress,
that shouldn't be a
problem, should it?
He's the rightful heir to the
throne of one of our allies.
We don't want him
to be too shrewd,
but if he's incompetent,
that won't work in
Clarines' favor, either.
If you wouldn't mind, I'd
like for you to give Raj
another pep talk
to motivate him.
You will remain in Tanbarun
for seven days.
Before you go, I want you to
train in court appearance
so as to not make a fool out
of yourself or Clarines.
Shirayuki, you will go
to Tanbarun in 14 days,
and that is an order.
[ZEN gasping]
[IZANA] I'm curious
as to your silence.
This little adventure is a
significant opportunity for you.
I can't imagine you
don't realize that.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
No, Prince Izana--
Lord Brother.
I have a request.
Will you permit me to add
one condition to this order?
Condition?
[ZEN] If this must
indeed come to pass,
I want someone to accompany
her to Tanbarun.
Someone I trust.
I refuse to concede this point.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[IZANA]
Very well.
Now, then, Shirayuki.
Will you go?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes. As you wish, Your Highness.
[MITSUHIDE] Interesting.
Shirayuki is going to Tanbarun.
Odd timing.
This in the same night we
find out some pretty boy
is trying to come kidnap her.
Where's Mihaya?
We ordered him to
stay at the castle.
He's under guard since he's
the only one who knows
what Kazuki looks like.
[ZEN]
Mitsuhide.
I want you to accompany
Shirayuki to Tanbarun
and watch out for her.
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes, sir.
[SERVANT A]
These will be your quarters
until you depart for Tanbarun.
I hope you will find
them to your liking.
Please make yourself
comfortable.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes. Thank you.
[SHIRAYUKI sighs]
I'm going to train for court.
And I'm going back to Tanbarun.
Not to mention all the Mihaya
and Kazuki weirdness.
What a day...
[ZEN]
I refuse to concede this point.
Zen.
[SHIRAYUKI] I can only do
what I can do right now.
[OBI] You and the master, you're
both always so dependable.
[MITSUHIDE] But it's more likely
he just wants to protect her.
[SHIRAYUKI] I wish I could
explain how talking to you
makes me feel better,
but I can't.
[OBI] I think the two of
us should have a match.