[GARAK] That must've
been difficult for you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
It wasn't too bad.
Luckily, Prince Zen and
the soldiers at Fort Laxdo
were very helpful.
[GARAK] Well, you should
be proud of your work.
[RYU]
Yeah, really good job there.
[GARAK] You can take
the rest of the day off.
I shouldn't, everyone
else is still working.
[RYU]
Getting rest is important, too.
Uh. As you wish.
All right. I guess
I'll be going, then.
See you later!
[door closes]
Shirayuki's really
pushing herself hard.
[RYU]
Yes, she is.
[GARAK] Speaking of which,
I wonder if she knows?
About what?
[GARAK]
About Prince Izana.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Another new encounter.
On this road I'm traveling.
[SHIRAYUKI]
This is the destiny I've chosen.
And where my dreams
become reality.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Today, I'll accompany Ryu
to the herb garden,
and I'll organize the medical
records right after that.
Oh, Zen!
Hi, Shirayuki. How are you...
Uh, something is different.
"Clarines Kingdom,
Wistal Castle,
Apprentice Court Herbalist."
You got your official ID!
[SHIRAYUKI] They finished making
it while we were at Fort Laxdo.
And my uniform.
[ZEN]
So I assume that you have
new accommodations
in the castle.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm-hm.
I have even more studying
and work to do, now.
I'll have a much easier
time doing it from here.
That's fair. I'll be
swamped too,
dealing with the aftermath
of the incident at the fort.
It may be quite a while
before we're able to
see each other again.
Uh! Oh, I see.
Shirayuki?
Okay, gotta go!
Just a minute! Doesn't that
bother you even a little bit?
Uh! Well, are you bothered?
Should I be?
Uh! Oh, fine, never mind.
[ZEN] All right, then.
Have fun, I'll see you!
We're waiting for
the investigation report
from the army for this.
Has the new fort communication
system been implemented?
[KIKI]
Yes, it has.
Excellent. Now, then.
Shall we go to the archives?
[MITSUHIDE] The soldiers
at the fort will need
to be on extra high alert now.
[KIKI]
Probably.
[ZEN] But, I know they
wanna do their best for me.
We just need to reinforce
the system to empower them.
[MITSUHIDE]
What's the matter?
[KIKI] The palace guard
stations... they've changed.
[MITSUHIDE] You're right. And
there are more of them, too.
[KIKI]
I wasn't notified of this.
[MITSUHIDE] Zen, hey, wait,
where are you going?
[OBI yawns]
Everyone else is busy,
which means all I
get to be is bored.
I'm restricted to
such a small area,
and I don't even have
weapons to clean or repair.
[SOLDIER A]
Prince Zen,
we cannot allow you
to proceed any further.
And why not?
I cannot answer that, sir.
[ZEN]
Very well, then. Thank you.
Kiki, Mitsuhide, make
yourselves presentable.
[KIKI, MITSUHIDE grunt]
[ZEN] Of course, I can't
speak until I'm spoken to.
Hey Obi, come here!
You have ten seconds.
[OBI] Wow. Why give
me so much time?
Listen, I need you to--
You have a scratch.
Oh, you mean this little thing?
It's a funny story, actually--
Please pardon me,
Your Highness.
What do you want?
[SERVANT A] I was told to
deliver this to you post haste.
[ZEN] Sorry, Obi. I'll have
to hear your story later.
For the moment, keep
your face uncovered.
Sure.
And wait for me in
this room. Got it?
[OBI]
Mm. Okay.
[SERVANT A]
Excuse me.
Shirayuki, the prince has
requested your presence.
Uh, all right. I'm coming.
[SERVANT 6A] Please go to the
Room of Chanting Flowers.
I'm sorry? To the
Room of what, now?
[ZEN]
I beg your pardon.
[door opens]
[footsteps]
[door closes]
Well hello, Little Brother.
It's been a long time,
Lord Brother.
I see you've brought
Mitsuhide and Kiki.
Always the faithful little
pair of guard dogs.
Indeed, I have.
Why didn't you inform
me you were returning?
I was just wondering when
your keen eye would notice me.
I wanted to see how
much attention
you actually pay to what
goes on in our castle.
[SERVANT A]
Please wait in here.
And refrain from
making any noise.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Okay?
[SHIRAYUKI] What is this?
What's going on?
[IZANA] I heard you traveled
all the way to Laxdo, Zen.
[ZEN]
Yes.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen?
[IZANA]
I saw the report, too.
It said every soldier
at the fort fell ill
because of some bandits.
They couldn't even move.
It must've been
extremely traumatic.
[SHIRAYUKI]
He's speaking so coldly to him.
Only someone with a
higher social status
would take such a tone.
It has to be the First
Prince of Clarines!
If what I've been
told is accurate,
you were only there with a court
herbalist and another attendant.
Why didn't you bring
this new servant here?
[ZEN] Because he is new
and I did not need him.
He's the one with the
wee scratch on his cheek.
I thought he was an outlaw, but
it seems he's in your employ.
Now, I didn't see a record
of any guards at the fort
receiving due punishment.
[ZEN]
I did not punish them.
Why not?
They patrol and protect
the surrounding lands.
It's an important duty.
The siege required
their assistance
and pulled them away from
this service for too long.
I felt it was time to return
them to their assigned post.
Oh, I see.
Then why don't we remove Laxdo
from your weak jurisdiction for,
let's say, six months?
[ZEN gasps]
[IZANA] Even if it was
the bandits' doing,
there were flaws in
the fort's system.
If you do not see fit to
rebuke the soldiers,
then you will receive
their punishment.
[MITSUHIDE] Which will shame
the soldiers far more
than the guilt they
already feel.
[KIKI] Zen can't be
taking this very well.
[IZANA] Someone with
such a soft underbelly
would naturally refuse to
be hard on anyone else.
That wouldn't be fair.
[ZEN]
I understand.
Good. Next on the docket...
[gasps]
[IZANA]
I've kept you waiting.
--[KIKI gasps]
--Shirayuki?
[IZANA] Zen, you and your two
toadies are dismissed, now.
Don't you have work to do?
What are you up to?
Zen...
[ZEN]
Fine, we're leaving.
See you later, Shirayuki.
Don't worry. I'll come find you.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Zen?
We'll talk soon, Lord Brother.
Mitsuhide, Kiki. Let's go.
[IZANA]
Hmph.
[SHIRAYUKI] So, you're, um...
You're Prince Zen's big brother.
Is that right?
[IZANA] What an adorable
way to address me.
Did you call me up here
because of the incident
at Laxdo you mentioned earlier?
[IZANA]
Hardly.
Uh?
Forgive me, then, because I
don't know why you sent for me.
You and Zen have a rather
special relationship.
I clearly see it.
It's odd for a royal to have
a commoner for a friend.
This would be interesting to
anyone who might hear about it.
I certainly thought it was.
There must be something
Zen finds alluring
and indispensable
about you, am I right?
I don't know. I can't judge
if people see me in that way.
The only thing I can
do is be myself.
Fair enough.
Sorry to keep you, dear.
You're free to go.
Yes, sir.
[IZANA] Now, if you're not
feigning all that humility.
One must then assume
Zen negligently invited
a foreign girl with rather
strange hair into our castle...
Which would make him an
awfully incompetent prince.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
What is it?
[MITSUHIDE] I dunno.
Can't help wondering.
What would your brother
want with Shirayuki?
[IZANA]
Did you hear that?
She referred to me as
'Zen's big brother'.
I found that terribly
amusing, truth to tell.
[IZANA] Now. Let's settle
this matter, shall we?
Ah. Can we go home?
[SASAKI] Why would you say
that? We've only just arrived.
Dummy, I'm saying it
because we're here at all!
Prince Izana made a concerted
effort to summon you today
for the purpose of
deepening your friendship.
Additionally, it will
fortify the accords
between your kingdoms.
Oh, I know!
But why invite me now,
after all this time?
[stomach growls]
[SASAKI] And now you're
pretending to be sick?
No, I'm not!
[whimpering]
[ZEN] Greetings, Prince
Raj, we welcome you.
I am the Second Prince
of Clarines, Zen Wisteria.
It is an honor and a pleasure.
Please pardon me.
Greetings to you.
I am Raj Schenazade of Tanbarun.
And I am pleased to make
your acquaintance.
Thank you very much.
[MITSUHIDE] I find it very
curious that Prince Izana
would invite Prince Raj here.
Oh come on, who wouldn't
want to meet a moronic
and selfish buffoon
who tried to force
a town girl to be his concubine
and then sent her poisoned
apples when she ran away?
[laughs] Sarcasm
suits you, Kiki.
But it was after he summoned
Shirayuki. Suspicious.
Yeah. Zen thinks there's a
reason behind it, as well.
Hm? What in the world
is that man up to?
I'm Prince Izana Wisteria.
Welcome to our humble
abode, Prince Raj.
Since we have finally
met face to face,
we should dispense with
further formalities.
Come, let's away to the garden.
See anything good?
[SHIRAYUKI yelps]
What are you doing up here, Obi?
[OBI] I got outa guard duty.
Thought I'd wander around.
The master and his servants
have really been actin'
strange lately.
Oh, yeah. You're originally
from Tanbarun, right?
Did something happen
between you and Prince Raj?
So I have a wicked idea.
It's actually the reason that
I came up here to get you!
Huh?
[OBI]
C'mon, let's go spy on 'em!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh?! Wait--
This makes me uncomfortable.
Do you want a berry?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm-mm.
Oh, good, we can hear them.
[HARUKA]
Prince Zen,
I hear you have a new
attendant in your court.
[ZEN] Yes, Lord Haruka.
Did my brother tell you that?
[HARUKA]
Indeed.
He is very nimble and skilled.
Both are valuable assets.
As long as he is prepared to
do battle when the time comes.
You must have a worthy adjutant.
Someone oblivious to his
surroundings will not suffice.
Zen!
[ZEN]
Izana.
[IZANA] I was wondering what
you might have discussed
during the welcome
reception at the gate.
We merely exchanged greetings.
[ZEN] This is true.
We've only just met.
Incidentally, Raj, I heard
that you recently fell
for a beautiful,
red-haired girl--
[choking]
This damsel of yours
is actually here.
She's in the castle as we speak.
You're kidding me. She is?
I mean. Who, again?
I think you know her name.
It was Shirayuki, wasn't it?
I don't like where
this is going.
I heard that the girl left you,
but perhaps you
still care for her.
If so, I'd be delighted
to invite her to join us.
[ZEN]
Lord Brother,
you are reading far
too deeply into this.
[IZANA] Am I? It seems
crystal clear to me.
Besides, the girl might want
to return to her home
country someday, you know.
That's quite enough!
My, my. This conversation is
certainly going downhill fast.
Uh? Still with me?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh, sorry.
M-My break's over.
I have to get back.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What were they trying to say?
Do they want me
to leave Clarines?
Maybe they think I'm
no longer useful.
[RAJ]
Uh...
[ZEN]
Speak, Raj.
[gasps]
[nervous chuckling]
Thank you kindly for
the offer, Prince Izana,
but I must politely decline.
Shirayuki definitely didn't
leave because of me.
That's a silly rumor.
She wanted to live
in another country,
and I wholeheartedly
gifted her my blessing
and support in so doing.
No affection to speak of!
Why are you so
hesitant to see her?
[RAJ yelps]
[RAJ]
Uh...
[ZEN] If you don't want
your deceptive actions
to be a matter of public record,
you must swear you'll stay
away from her. Forever.
Don't you even dare to
say her name out loud.
[RAJ whimpering]
Okay, okay! I promise,
please! Cross my heart!
[clears throat]
Well, this is what I have heard.
Zen considers Shirayuki
to be his fiancée,
and he says they will
soon be married!
[HARUKA gasping]
[ZEN]
Let's have a chat.
[RAJ]
Uh! Uh. Ow, that's my arm.
Is this a statement
we should believe?
I believe I'm going to vomit.
[RAJ groans]
Care to explain yourself,
Prince Moron?
[RAJ]
Hey, come on!
I had no choice with the way
the conversation was going!
[ZEN]
Yes, you did!
[RAJ] All right, I might have
exaggerated things a little bit
for effect, but you know
the core of it is the truth!
How so?
[RAJ] You and Shirayuki
are obviously lovers.
Wait a minute. Are you telling
me that you're not?!
Keep your voice down.
[RAJ]
Big problem!
[ZEN]
And why do you care?
[RAJ]
Because if that's really true,
then there'll be no
way to guarantee
that she won't
eventually leave you!
Remember, she knows I'm the
one who poisoned those apples!
I need to be able to keep
a close eye on her.
If you don't want
Shirayuki, that's fine.
I can assure you,
I will valiantly attempt
to make her happy.
What?
[RAJ]
It's apparent that this is
what Prince Izana
would prefer as well.
Of course, she would be treated
with nothing but
courtesy in my castle--
Rejected.
[RAJ]
He-heh.
[RAJ] But wait! You haven't
heard the rest of it.
[ZEN]
For your information,
Shirayuki is not
currently in this castle
to hide what happened
between you that day.
[gasps]
[ZEN]
You're right.
I cannot possibly guarantee
that Shirayuki will stay
with me in the future.
But to clarify, I remain hopeful
in the absence of a promise.
We always want what
we don't have.
So we keep striving for it.
[HARUKA] Hm? Ah, Prince Zen.
Can you explain this nonsense?
A simple misunderstanding.
Raj was jumping to
silly conclusions.
The truth is,
I do not consider Shirayuki my
fiancée, nor have I proposed.
[bell tolls]
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'm going to head out now.
[RYU]
Good work today.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I guess that's it. Raj is here.
How long is he going to stay?
And what'll I do if I have to
go with him when he leaves?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I don't want to go.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
I'm so confused.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'm at a loss.
I can't say if I would benefit
or harm him in the
future by staying.
And that makes me wonder
why I'm here now.
Which would make him an
awfully incompetent prince.
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's just like before.
I had no answer, then,
and I don't have one now.
[gasps]
[ZEN]
Shirayuki...
[ZEN] What is the place you're
planning on going by yourself?
[SHIRAYUKI] The reason I'm
staying in this country.
I want to know it.
See how the rest of
you live in Clarines.
Find out where I belong.
That's the place
where I'm going.
The place where I'll be at home.
Well, when you're there.
I hope I'll still be able
to see you anyway.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI panting]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki, what happened?
[IZANA] So tell me, princess.
Have you come to dislike it?
[ZEN] He was the firstborn,
and as such, a priority.
[KIKI] Our little prince
is starting to grow up.
[ZEN] And remember,
I'm always on your side.