This rain just came
out of nowhere.
We've almost made
it to the border,
but we won't make it back
to the castle tonight.
We'll have to find somewhere
to stay until tomorrow, then.
There's an inn not
too far ahead of us.
Do you want to check there?
Sure.
Shirayuki. Are you all right?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yep!
[ZEN]
Okay, let's try to get there
before it starts raining harder.
[OBI, MITSUHIDE, KIKI]
Yes, sir!
[INNKEEPER A]
Caught in the rain as well?
Will two three-person rooms
be acceptable to you?
Yes, thank you. Anything's fine.
[INNKEEPER A] I imagine you'll
all want a bath, first?
Please, make yourselves at home.
Oh, a bath sounds
great right now.
Yes, that should
warm us up nicely.
[TROW] Ugh, what is this
rain trying to prove?
[sighs] Any rooms?
Yes, of course.
I'll be right with you.
Gotta love these
blessed rains.
[gasps]
[OBI] We're lucky they
had rooms left, huh?
[ZEN]
Yeah.
[OBI]
You know, Master.
Well... I heard
Miss Kiki and Shirayuki
are in the bath next
door to us right now.
[ZEN gasps]
[OBI]
Huh?
Why would you even
bring that up?!
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't realize
there were rules about what
we could discuss in here.
You're a funny one, Master.
[OBI]
Maybe this will be better:
I feel bad that Mitsuhide
didn't get to join us.
[ZEN] We couldn't all be
unarmed at the same time.
When they're with me, it
doesn't matter where we are,
they're working.
I know Miss Kiki and Mitsuhide's
responsibility is you, but,
the way they act together makes
me think that they're betrothed.
Obi. What is with your
choice of topics right now?
I thought it'd be nice
to talk about them.
If they were betrothed, I
certainly wouldn't be upset.
If they say they're happy,
and I can see it's true,
I think that would be wonderful.
[OBI] How could you
"see it's true", though?
Same goes for you.
[gasps]
Well, this is kind of awkward.
Whenever I think of you
saying those sweet words,
I won't be able to help but
to picture you naked, as well.
You're impossible!
Just forget it.
I'm done with you.
Way too late for that.
Eventually, I'm gonna
think about it.
Well, Master.
Shall we try to find a
spot where we can peek
in on the ladies?
Stop it!
[OBI laughs]
Calm down, Master.
I was just kidding.
You're so gullible.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Kiki, do you all stay in places
like this a lot when you travel?
[KIKI] Only when Zen prefers
to keep his identity a secret.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, that makes sense.
[KIKI] It's because Zen
thinks it's important to see
what's beyond the court.
When he was younger,
he felt caged in by those
big castle windows,
so he likes to escape
'em every now and then.
Caged in, huh?
I suppose that could make you
want to escape anything.
[KIKI] You've been with us
for a while now, haven't you?
[SHIRAYUKI]
She's too bright!
[KIKI]
Hm?
Here! So sorry about that wait.
[OBI] Hey, if it's not
too much trouble,
would you bring me
somethin' nice and spicy?
[WAITRESS A]
Sure, no problem!
This is good. We can't get
food like this normally.
Why not try making
it at the castle?
Don't be ridiculous.
You know, as long as
I have the recipe,
I could probably make it.
She could, too.
I guess so.
At the very least, I could
get pretty close.
Do you mind giving it a try?
I can help you out
if you'd like me to.
Seriously? I didn't realize
you knew how to cook.
[MITSUHIDE]
I do. Before I came here,
we used to take
turns making meals.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Really?
[MITSUHIDE]
I picked up a few things.
[OBI]
Uh, oh.
Well, great, I'm the only
one who doesn't cook.
C'mon, give yourself a break,
you are just a prince.
Here.
Have a bite, Master!
Obi!
How can you speak in such
a way toward your master?
Listen, the prince and I
trust each other implicitly.
Would you like
to challenge that?
Because I'm game.
--[MITSUHIDE] Zen!
--[OBI] Master.
You have to choose only one!
--[MITSUHIDE] Choose wisely!
--[OBI] Choose mine!
You first!
[BOTH]
Right.
We apologize tremendously.
[laughing]
[ALL]
Uh?
We haven't been like
this for too long.
Way too long! [laughs]
Very true. I can't
remember the last time
we could all just have
a good time together.
[TROW]
Excuse me, there, sir.
I saw you earlier
at the inn, didn't I?
Yes, you'd been caught
in the rain, too, right?
[TROW]
Well, hello, there, handsome.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh...
You're not free tonight
by chance, are you?
I can thank you for remembering.
It's fine. No.
Hey, little help?
Oh, excuse me. I didn't
know he was yours.
That man is not mine. He's free.
[MITSUHIDE]
Kiki!
So, Mitsuhide's
popular with women?
I guess.
The castle maids were all
excited when he first showed up.
I assume it's because
he looks nice.
No. I appreciate it,
but I need to stay here.
Really? What a shame.
How 'bout that one?
He seems elegant,
which is different.
[ZEN gasps]
[TROW] But not you. You look
like you'd be dangerous.
[OBI]
How can ya tell?
[TROW]
Not to brag,
but I have a pretty
good eye for men.
Well, let me know if you
change your mind, handsome!
I think that girl
would take anyone.
Anyone other than me,
to be specific.
Or me!
[ZEN]
Still early!
[OBI] I wonder if it's
stopped raining, yet?
I'll go take a look.
[TROW]
The sky is beautiful tonight.
The moon is nice and clear
and those stars...
[SHIRAYUKI sighs] I think
I might've eaten too much.
Look, it's stopped raining.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank goodness.
Everything in Tanbarun
has been so hectic.
It's nice to have a break,
even if it wasn't
what we'd planned.
You all deserve to relax.
You've had to be dependable and
brave practically non-stop.
If anyone's earned a night
off, it's the two of you.
You know, Obi,
you've said something
like that before.
That I deserved to relax
because I'm always
trying to play it strong.
Oh, you mean that time when
you got really drunk?
I can't believe
you remembered that.
We get to relax, as
long as you're here.
Then, we can share
our strengths.
[OBI]
Mm!
At least, that's what it
feels like, so thank you.
You know it's true. Come on.
Zen, you feel the same?
[ZEN]
About you, yes.
I'm different, though.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, I doubt that.
[laughing]
Did we say something
to laugh at?
Uh. No, not that I'm aware of...
I don't know, myself.
Seriously, I have no idea
why I'm laughing right now.
When I'm with you two, it
always ends up like this.
[MITSUHIDE]
So, you went to the baths
with Shirayuki, didn't you?
You girls have fun?
Uh! Sorry! Words came out wrong.
I didn't mean it that way.
It's just that you and Shirayuki
haven't had the chance
to spend much time alone before.
She was the same as usual.
Didn't turn into another
person or anything.
Zen's like that.
They don't change based
on their audience.
And that's a good thing?
Yes, of course.
Yeah, I feel the same way.
I've talked to Zen
about it before.
The two of you haven't
changed since you met,
have you? Even though
your relationship has.
You think? I don't know
because at first,
she was a lot colder
to me than anyone else.
Well, you acted a lot more
arrogant than anyone else.
You shut up!
If we haven't changed,
it's because of Shirayuki.
She knows who she is.
Even after telling her
I was really a prince,
she stayed the same person
she's always been.
She inspires me to
be true to myself.
No matter what happens, I
think we'll always be close.
As if I have a choice.
[MITSUHIDE]
And he's right.
It sounds as if Zen will be able
to leave your nest
soon, Mitsuhide.
[laughs] Well, even if he does,
he'll still be my
first priority.
And that's why Zen worries.
He has every reason to be
afraid you'll be alone
for the rest of your life, too.
Because you say stuff like that.
What?! He's afraid
I'll wind up alone?
Not just him.
Right. I'm not that worried.
I just need to find
someone who also sees Zen
as a priority and marry them.
So, like Obi?
[MITSUHIDE] No, that thought
didn't even cross my mind.
[OBI] Well, I'm gonna have
another drink before I head in.
Have a good night, Miss.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thanks.
He's great, but I wish
he'd be a little more
self-aware, you know?
Oh. I'm sorry.
You're fine.
Ten seconds.
Right.
Who knew the rain would leave
behind old acquaintances?
You've certainly changed, Obi.
You think so?
[TROW]
The people that you're with
seemed most likely
to be swordsmen.
Are they your current employers?
[OBI] I suppose you could
call one my master.
Your Master? How cute.
You're still as sharp as ever.
Yeah, thanks. Why are
you in Tanbarun?
I'm looking for someone.
Someone who ran all the way
from Clarines, in fact.
Care to help me out, here?
It could be like old times.
Of course you would say that.
Not that I wasn't
expecting this.
It's been three years.
I wish you would've
expected a tryst
or something fun like that.
[OBI] Really, Trow?
Do you truly care for me?
If I did, we'd surely be sharing
a tearful embrace, dear.
It's darling.
Oh, and if you're asking me
to take part in a crime,
apologies, but that's
not my style, now.
[TROW]
Come on, it's nothing bad.
Just finding someone
who ran away from home.
I finally had a lead on the kid,
too. Until the rain started.
We're old friends, aren't we?
[OBI] Hm... If it's quick and
just for the night, I'll do it.
[TROW] There are a lot of rumors
floating around about you, Obi.
Some thought you must've
gone into hiding.
While others believed you'd
settled down with a family
or just kicked the bucket.
People can say whatever
they want about me.
[TROW] I knew you had
to at least be alive.
You're hardly the type who's
likely to make fatal mistakes.
I wonder.
[TROW]
This is it.
That place has been
empty for a year.
And yet, we have a light.
Almost like they're trying to
let us to know where they are.
Thank goodness for amateurs.
Who's the runaway?
[TROW]
Son of some rich man.
Apparently, he wasn't
very happy about whatever,
so he ran away from home.
Some people are too rich
for their own good.
[OBI] Hm... I have to be
back by morning, Trow.
[TROW]
And if you aren't?
[OBI]
I'll probably get scolded.
[TROW] We can't have that!
It'll be quick.
[MITSUHIDE]
Zen, hey.
[ZEN]
Uh...
[MITSUHIDE]
Can we talk?
Uh?
What do you mean Obi isn't back?
He left a note for us that said
he would be out a bit longer.
You didn't hear
anything, did you?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Nothing.
[ZEN growls]
I cannot believe that guy.
Here we go.
[TROW] That's our entry point.
Give me another boost.
[OBI] So, basically,
I'm here as a stepladder?
Hey! Try to be louder!
[TROW]
It's fine.
Now, according to what I've been
told, he's hired some guards.
So I'm counting on you to
take care of them for me.
Thanks, Obi!
Right. I remember why I
stopped working with you.
[GUARD A]
What are you doing here?
Who are you?
Relax, I was just
passin' through, friend.
And the last thing I'm
lookin' for is a fight.
You found one anyway! [groans]
Whoa.
So you're kinda bad at
listening and fighting, huh?
[yelps]
You must be Kido Deena.
My clients are looking
for you, sweetheart.
I'm not gonna go
home, all right!
Leave me alone!
[TROW]
Oh, I don't care about that.
My clients are the guards
you hired on the way here.
They're none to happy you
left without paying them.
[KIDO]
Uh!
I'm curious now, though, why
did you run away from home?
I left because I don't
have any freedom there.
They have too many rules, and I
don't want to succeed my father!
[TROW]
Mm. That sounds awful for you.
[KIDO]
I have money!
If I pay you,
will you let me go?
Wow, are you really
trying to bribe me?
[KIDO whimpering]
[KIDO yelps]
Don't act so spoiled.
You get to take responsibility
for your poor
decisions this time.
If you don't like it,
then stay home when
you get sad, Rich Boy.
You'll be safe, there.
[KIDO whimpering]
[KIDO groans]
[TROW] You're a man, right?
You should be able to take this.
[KIDO sighs]
[yawns]
[door opens]
Huh?
Oh, my, so there were
more of you, then?
[GUARD B] Who do you
think you are, woman?
[GUARD B groans]
[TROW]
Uh!
[OBI]
Idiot!
[TROW gasping]
[TROW] Ow, ow. Not my
finest hour, was it?
How are you, any injuries?
Yeah, no. This is nothing.
Makes me think of the old days.
We did more than a few
jobs together back then.
[OBI]
Yes, that happened.
I remember how you'd talk to
anyone without hesitation.
But you never let
yourself get attached.
So you were easy to work with.
Oh, yeah.
You were only hurt once that
I know of, but it was bad.
Obi! Oh my god.
We need to get you help.
I'm fine.
And we got the job done, right?
[chuckles]
[TROW]
Obi!
[TROW] I thought you were so
dangerous at the time, too.
Hey, we could pick up
where we left off.
Wanna work together again?
Oh, no, is it too late?
They say if you stop
in one place,
your body gets
weighted down there.
Is that what's going on?
You can at least grunt
in my direction, here.
It's like I'm not complete,
like I left a part of me
behind with those people.
And that part is utterly
under their control.
I can't do anything of my own
free will without it, either.
Although, I don't
really mind it.
So, that means what?
I wonder.
Well, I wonder more.
I never knew you to be one
to work under a master.
I think I see a light
moving over there.
[TROW]
Huh? There shouldn't be.
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
I'm sorry.
I was planning to go
right back, Master, but--
[ZEN]
But what?!
[OBI]
How's the runaway doing?
Don't worry about me.
I'm gonna go home
where I can be safe.
[OBI] Yay, happy endings. I
can't believe you found me here.
Consider it luck.
Yesterday, when Kiki
checked the area,
she saw a light and thought
it seemed suspicious.
We were only hoping
you'd be here.
If you weren't, I don't know
if you'd've ever been found.
Understood, Sir.
You came, too, Miss?
You know what you're doing.
Are you like a healer
or something?
Uh, well, I'm actually
an herbalist.
Same thing if you ask me.
Thank you so much.
[SHIRAYUKI]
My pleasure.
[ZEN] I didn't realize you
two knew each other.
Why not say anything?
[OBI] In that line of work,
it was normal to pretend
not to know each other
no matter where we were.
Habit.
[ZEN]
I understand.
Master, are you jealous?
What...?
Uh. Never mind,
forget I said it.
Obi, this is a good time
to tell you something.
You need to be more self-aware.
[OBI]
Huh?
[ZEN] There are people
who tend to worry
if you're not where
you're supposed to be.
I'm one of them.
If you can't understand that,
then, next time I won't
go looking for you.
I'm so sorry.
[ZEN]
Mm...
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi!
I want to look at where your
shoulder was cut. Let me see.
No, don't worry about me.
This is nothing.
[ZEN, SHIRAYUKI growl]
[OBI]
Okay, okay, I'll show you.
[ZEN] I'll let Mitsuhide and
Kiki know what happened.
[SHIRAYUKI]
All right.
Ow, be gentle. So uh, you're
mad at me, right Miss?
No, I'm just relieved.
You're obviously
angry right now.
What can I say?
"Don't make us worry" like
I'm any better than you are?
If anyone understands
this, it's me.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi, that scar on your chest.
[OBI gasping]
[SHIRAYUKI]
It looks serious.
[OBI] I wonder. It happened
a long time ago.
Uh!
If you had been able
to treat me like this,
I would never have
scarred so badly.
I'm sorry I didn't come back
sooner. Won't happen again.
Great. That sounds perfect.
I'll wait for you
outside, all right?
[OBI]
All right, Miss.
Hm?
Is that honestly Obi in there?
I don't get what's going
on at all. Do you?
[OBI]
I wonder.
[ZEN] Obi, if you can move
okay, we're going back!
I'm good. Let's go.
[OBI]
How should I know?
[MITSUHIDE] Did you give
Obi a good scolding?
No, not exactly. I should have.
Shirayuki's never ridden on
my horse before, has she?
[MITSUHIDE]
When we're all together,
we can't very well make the
prince carry her, can we?
No, I suppose not.
He wants her to ride with him.
I know.
She was an interesting woman.
I didn't think to ask
for her name, though.
I'm not sure if this is her
real name, but... it's Trow.
To be honest, I don't think
we'll see her again.
Why not?
Because of me.
I have no interest in being the
kind of person I was back then,
before Master took my reins.
[SHIRAYUKI] I'd like to
see that version of you.
[OBI] What?! Be careful
what you wish for,
you could get burned.
[SHIRAYUKI]
But I have medicine for that!
[IZANA]
All of these are requests
for marriage
interviews with Zen?
[ZEN]
The intent to take a wife?
[KIKI] Well, we have spent
quite a long time together
while keeping an eye
out for each other.
[IZANA] I've always been this
soft on my brother, haven't I?