[ZEN]
Atri.
You had everything I didn't.
A roof over you. All the
food you could ever eat.
You were born into a life I'd
never know no matter what I did.
It disgusts me that you
did nothing to deserve this.
You took things for granted.
And you'll die for it!
No matter what you think of me.
You were my friend.
And that's how
I'll remember you.
[MITSUHIDE growls]
[ATRI groans]
Atri.
I wonder, Prince, if... if you
hadn't been born into this.
Would things have
turned out better?
[ZEN] At some point
in all of our lives,
we long for a
genuine connection.
But we cannot stray from
the paths we travel.
So when we discover a soul
who inspires and moves us,
who speaks to our heart.
We hold on to that person.
Look at that.
Well, how is she?
[OBI]
Awake.
[GARAK] She still looks a
little bit drunk to me.
[OBI]
Yes, she does.
I have to go back to the office
and finish up some work,
so if you don't mind, could
you look after her for a bit?
[footsteps]
Sure, I'm fairly certain
I can handle that.
How are you feelin',
Miss? Any better?
[OBI]
Hm?
[knocking]
[GARAK]
Yes?
Excuse me. Chief herbalist,
is Obi here, by chance?
You mean he wasn't
with Shirayuki?
I had asked him to keep
a close eye on her.
[KIKI] Keep an eye on her?
Did something happen?
Uh, no, no. She, just...
[clears throat]
I offered her an alcoholic
beverage as a good-natured joke,
but then she passed out.
It would seem she can't
quite handle her liquor,
it was clear that she
needed to sleep it off
for a while so she
could sober up.
[KIKI]
In the bunk room?
[GARAK]
Mm-hm.
Shirayuki wasn't
in there, either.
[GARAK]
Hm?
All I found was this
note written to Zen.
Wonderful.
She shouldn't be alone.
I hope Obi went with her.
[KIKI]
He must have.
As long as she's with a
prince-approved guardian,
I think she'll be fine.
[OBI] Hey! You still
look sort of unsteady.
[SOLDIER A]
What? That girl is down there.
[SOLDIER B]
Hm?
[SOLDIER A] You know, Prince
Zen's pretty new fiancée.
[SOLDIER B]
Huh? Where?
[SOLDIER C]
So that's really her?
[SOLDIER A]
What an unusual shade of red!
[SOLDIERS stammering]
[OBI]
Hm.
Oh, well. So much for people
not gossiping about her.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Jackets, household medicines
they were running out of,
but, wait a second...
I never learned how to
ride a horse! [cries]
[OBI]
Say what?
[SHIRAYUKI]
That's right.
Mitsuhide let me ride
with him before. Heh.
If I had an older brother, I
think he'd be like Mitsuhide.
Okay, so it seems she's
really drunk, still.
[SHIRAYUKI]
A horse!
[OBI]
A horse? What for?
Be honest, do you wanna
go back to Tanbarun?
Look! There's Lord Haruka!
C'mon, why aren't you looking?
[OBI] Nice try, but it's
the middle of the night,
he's not there.
Besides, I'm not takin'
my eyes off you.
You've been guarding
me all day?
Even when I fell
asleep after I got...
drunk?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh.
Thank you.
[OBI laughs]
I know it's not the same
as if it were the
Prince, though.
[SHIRAYUKI growls]
What? Am I wrong here?
If Zen spent an
entire day with me,
Lord Haruka would be
absolutely furious.
Oh, yeah, That's true.
We gotta go.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Uh... Uh!
[MAN A]
Damn. I think he spotted me.
I need to finish this
report and get out of here.
Can you wait for
me in this spot?
Um, sure.
[OBI chuckles]
[whistles]
[MAN A grunts]
Wha...?
"Red. There was contact.
The sun set, and no
wind was blowing."
"Red." Means Shirayuki.
Does "there was contact"
actually mean she had
a rendezvous
with Prince Zen?
According to this,
you're the only creep
who was spying on her today.
Speak up, who hired you?
[MAN A] I... I don't know
what you're talking about.
I found that tube
lying on the ground,
I just thought it was garbage.
[OBI]
Hmph. Great story!
How about I have you tell the
rest of it to the palace guard?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi!
[KIKI]
Well, goodnight, Highness.
[IZANA]
I must admit.
That's an unorthodox way
to gather companions.
It's on track to be
extremely difficult,
but you're the ones who
will have to weather it.
Yes, sir.
Uh, are you okay?
More okay than you, Miss.
What's that mean?
Master said this
would happen, right?
That people would come
out of the woodwork
in swarms to investigate you?
They shouldn't bother. They
aren't going to learn anything.
Yeah. Well, some folks are far
more persistent than others.
[OBI]
I have a question.
How do you think master's doing?
I mean, with his
princely duties?
From what I can see,
he's trying to be himself.
Uh? That's your answer?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Indeed, it is.
Look, he was noble even
when we'd just met.
He obviously loves his country.
Plus, he has Kiki and Mitsuhide.
Zen can't help it that
he's always been a prince
and that some people will always
try to take advantage of it.
I see no reason to hold
it against you now.
After all, when you left I
thought you might not come back.
But you did.
You've earned my trust.
[OBI] Yeah, I get where
you're comin' from,
but I think you being
here is affecting him
more than you may realize.
Affecting him how?
Please don't tell me my
presence has been a problem!
Mm! Sorry, what?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Wait, that's not funny.
What do you mean?
Mostly, I keep hearing
that everyone
is making fun of Prince Zen
because I spend so much time
with him. I'm only
making things worse.
[OBI] Tell me, Miss! What are
you actually mad about here?
Well, even though I fully
understand what the problem is,
I'm angry at myself because I
don't know how to fix it yet!
For example, the
Laxdo punishment!
[IZANA]
Oh, I see.
Then why don't
we remove Laxdo
from your weak jurisdiction
for, let's say, six months?
It still upsets me,
but I'm not certain if it's
worth going back there.
[OBI] Aha. Then you were
planning to go to Fort Laxdo?
That explains why you were
mumbling about jackets,
and medicine, and a horse.
Zen... Zen said he was fine.
But when he grabbed my hand,
he held it a lot
tighter than usual.
Playing strong, always.
[gasps]
And now we've gone back to
talking about the master.
It seems to me you
have the same need
to pretend everything's fine
most of the time too, Miss.
If you aren't sure what to do,
there's only one
way to find out.
Instead of waiting for
something to happen,
I suggest you get up
and take action.
But, you shouldn't attempt
the venture on your own,
like you did just now.
There was a suspicious
person around.
[sighs] Yeah, guess
you're right.
[OBI]
If no one's there to stop her,
she'll jump into things
without thinking.
The exact same way Master does.
The ironic part is,
there's no way for her to
know that when she's alone.
[OBI] If you really
want to go to Laxdo,
then I'll take you there myself.
However, you should know,
I already went back
pretty recently.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Master and his aides
were worried about it,
and everyone at the fort
took exceptional care of me.
So when I got castle leave,
I went to check on 'em.
On that note, here. For you.
My goodness, this
is a sekko plant.
It can only grow under snow!
It must be a pretty
hard herb to find.
That little kid at Laxdo,
Shuka, is that his name?
He's the one who picked it.
Shuka did that?
[SHIRAYUKI] A progress report
of everyone's current condition.
Wow, this is
incredibly detailed!
[OBI]
Will that help you out?
[SHIRAYUKI] Mm-hm. Yes, it
will. It's like a road map!
Oh. Guess the trip
wasn't too hard, then.
Well, it's easier when you
know how to ride a horse.
Takes an animal to know one.
What does that mean?
They gave me messages.
So many, in fact, that
I forgot a few of them.
But they all said
the same thing.
"We'll work hard... together."
That's great.
[SHIRAYUKI] Which means I
need to work just as hard.
Thanks for doing that, Obi!
[OBI]
Me?
All right then, let's go back.
Oh...
Uh-oh.
Hey! Be careful!
Crap!
You're still three sheets
to the wind. My, my, my.
It's fascinating to watch
the show you all put on.
Even if I am only
a mere spectator.
Up we go!
So Zen can't help it, huh?
Boy, is this a problematic
place to spectate.
[sighs]
I'm finally back. So sorry.
Kiki, you're awfully late.
Zen, look.
What is it?
When I went to check
on them, I found this.
[ZEN]
I'll be back.
[ZEN] Oh, yeah, Kiki.
Did you get it?
[MITSUHIDE]
Hey, wait! Zen...
[KIKI] He went to
look for Shirayuki.
Is she missing?
What happened to her?
That note must bear bad news.
Obi's the one who wrote it.
Apparently, Shirayuki
had been drunk earlier,
and passed out cold.
[laughs]
So that's why he practically
flew outa here. [laughs]
Oh...
But how'd she even
manage to get drunk?
That's not like her.
Obi was with her,
and Zen's on his way,
so I'm sure it'll be fine.
You're right.
I won't worry, then.
I'm glad she came to
join us. She fits well.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh.
[ZEN] Has it really
been an entire month
since I've set foot outside?
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes, sir.
And now that your
house arrest is over,
I have something
important for you.
[gasps]
[MITSUHIDE] Since the poor
boy doesn't have a grave,
we kept this.
The point of his arrow.
Atri.
[ZEN]
If I'm being honest,
I always knew in the
back of my mind
that his story never added up.
[MITSUHIDE]
I did, as well.
I wanted to believe...
I kept ignoring my doubts.
Prince Zen, know you are
a scion of this kingdom.
Among all who may
cross your path,
there will be people you
can trust eventually.
If you're suspicious
of everyone,
then everyone will
be your nemesis.
You should learn who
your allies are, first,
before assuming you
have nothing but enemies.
Try not to rush into
anything blindly.
[ZEN gasps]
As a prince of the
Clarines kingdom,
you will soon grow to learn
what is most important.
Take your time.
Be kind to yourself.
I am inexperienced, as well.
But I will remain by your side,
and become a man you
can always rely on.
[MITSUHIDE]
Please, allow me to protect you.
[ZEN]
Mitsuhide!
[MITSUHIDE gasps]
He said my name.
[ZEN]
I will become one, too.
[MITSUHIDE]
What do you mean, sir?
[ZEN]
I mean, I will become a master
his attendants can be proud of.
You've inspired me.
That's all. So, let's go.
'Kay?
[MITSUHIDE gasps]
Yes, I'm with you!
I've lightened up, Prince?
[laughs]
Stop it, that laugh is creepy.
Uh! My laugh is not creepy!
I was just remembering the time
Zen was making fun of me,
and he called me Grandpa
because I kept referring to him
by his formal title.
Oh yeah, that was pretty funny.
By the way, besides the note,
what did you toss to
Zen as he was leaving?
Just something he wanted me to
retrieve for him. You'll see.
[ZEN panting]
[OBI]
Uh.
Master!
Obi. You scoundrel!
I thought you'd be
in the medical wing.
Don't leave your post!
I was looking for you!
[panting]
Is she sleeping?
Yes. She still has some
alcohol left in her system.
I got word from the guards.
They said you apprehended
someone suspicious?
Right. A man sent
to spy on Shirayuki.
As you said, this kind
of thing would happen.
She did admit to me
that she sensed people
were secretly
watching her of late.
Not long ago,
she'd have tried to do something
about that herself.
[ZEN] She actually wanted
to return to Laxdo?
[OBI]
Yes. But she was drunk,
she can't ride a horse,
and I wouldn't let her go.
[ZEN] I get it.
She was worried about me.
Why don't you two just
go back there together?
When you're busy working, six
months will pass by in a blink.
[ZEN]
Heh.
[OBI] Anyway, I hope you're
not mad, but in her state,
I had to pick her up
and carry her back.
I didn't say anything,
did I?! Drop it, already.
Hey, you looked like you
were about to snap at me.
[ZEN]
No, I didn't!
It's interesting.
I said she could send
you away if she wanted.
But, she clearly decided not to.
Obi.
You did a great job.
[OBI]
Um, thanks.
It was a close call, though.
[ZEN]
Oh, was it?
Well, you were up
against Shirayuki.
If she had reason to, I'm sure
she'd even send me away.
Here, this is for you.
You've earned it.
A gift for me?
Identification?
I had it specially created.
The Official Messenger for the
Second Prince of Clarines.
That'll be your new title.
You sure about this?
Should getting a formal
title be this easy?
There was nothing
easy about it!
I feel like I'm starting
to understand.
I'm learning what matters
most to me in life.
And I want to try to
be a better prince.
[OBI]
Huh?
[ZEN]
I believe I can do it now.
I have faith in myself.
And in my friends.
Even in you, Obi.
[OBI] Master, I never noticed
how beautiful your eyes are.
[ZEN growls] I'm trying
to be serious here!
[OBI]
Hey, so why did you appoint me
your official messenger,
rather than make me
Shirayuki's guardian?
Well, I'm happy you asked.
Because no one else
needs to know you're more
than just my messenger.
It's sort of a decoy.
In other words, I'm Shirayuki's
first line of defense.
So if anything should
happen to her,
you'll be the first to know.
Right. And if people think
you're only working for me,
they won't get nosy.
Nobody will be the wiser.
[OBI]
Understood.
I swear. I'm going to be better,
and I will protect those that
are most important to me.
I think Zen might be
out for the night.
He's probably still
talkin' to Obi.
The stars are so
beautiful right now.
[KIKI] Uh. Yeah, but then
again, they always are.
[MITSUHIDE]
True.
How do you feel
about coming with me
to go get some exercise?
[KIKI]
I'd love to.
[ZEN] Time marches on.
And days turn into months.
Although this world
is ever-changing,
there are a few things I can
count on to never waver.
[ZEN]
There are people that I trust.
Who will stay
faithfully by my side.
And I stay by theirs.
[ZEN] As we continue
traveling together
on this path we've chosen.
[KIHAL]
Those higher classes
do like to look down
on folks like us.
[SHIRAYUKI]
That's the most beautiful bird
I've ever laid eyes on!
[IZANA]
When the time comes,
how will he protect
what's important?
[SHIRAYUKI] I still have to try
to do the right thing here!
No matter what it might cost me!