[SHIRAYUKI] I have to
stop falling asleep here.
How lovely.
[SHIRAYUKI]
The sun is shining on everything
in this town I've
chosen, including me.
That warmth nourishes
the choice I've made,
and illuminates
new feelings within.
See?
Hi, Shirayuki!
Well, hello, there!
Are you back to visit
Prince Zen today?
I'm not.
Mitsuhide and Kiki wanted
to see me this time.
So, um... There's something
I've been wondering about.
What's with the pendant that
old man wore around his neck?
[SHILA] Oh. That's just
his identification.
Identification?
[SHILA] Everyone who works
in the castle has to have it.
Nobody is allowed to enter the
gates under any circumstance
unless they're wearing one.
Oh. You're the
exception, Shirayuki.
The prince gave us
special orders.
[SHILA] Go ahead. You can
wait at the entrance.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank you very much!
[KAI]
She hangs out with the Prince!
Shirayuki's amazing, isn't she?
Come on. We should
get back to work.
[chuckles] Don't act like
you don't agree with me.
[SERVANTS chuckling]
[SOLDIER A] Greetings, my lord.
Are you here to see the prince?
[HARUKA]
Yes.
I apologize for
the inconvenience,
but he currently
has another visitor.
A visitor?
Of course it's her. Again.
They're more
beautiful every day!
[HARUKA]
Nothing about her appearance
shows her social status.
How am I to know if
this red-haired girl
is worthy of his friendship?
Red is a vulgar color.
[MITSUHIDE]
I'm glad you came so quickly.
We asked you to be here because
we need your help with Zen.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Is something wrong with him?
[MITSUHIDE]
He left on official business
outside the castle the other day
then snuck off to
check out the local area.
[SHIRAYUKI]
He snuck off?
Well, everybody around here
is used to him doing that.
[chuckles]
[MITSUHIDE] But this time he
was really late coming back
and he didn't clear it
with the ministers.
From what I gathered,
they were a lot harder on
him than they usually are.
So that's what's wrong
with him? Depression?
[MITSUHIDE chuckles]
[MITSUHIDE]
No, not really.
It's more like he's acting
like a baby about it
by locking himself
away in his office
and overworking
out of pure spite.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki?
Am I dreaming?
No.
I'm not a dream, but I
take that as a compliment.
Zen. Bringing Shirayuki
here was my idea.
Since you would rather spend
time with her than sleep...
You're the one who said that.
I only said it because you guys
wouldn't get off my back!
[KIKI]
She's all you could talk about.
You even wrote her name
on a couple of documents.
Go spend time with her.
I just like her name.
Well, if you don't want all
your replies to say "Shirayuki,"
you should take a bre--
Mitsuhide, you and I need
to have a talk later.
Okay. Maybe I should
just go home.
Sorry for interrupting--
[SHIRAYUKI]
What?
[ZEN]
You guys are being unfair.
[BOTH]
We realize that, Sir.
[ZEN] I'm sorry they
made you come out here.
[SHIRAYUKI] It's all right.
Are you having a hard time?
[ZEN] Yeah, but just 'cause
I was gone too long.
I don't wanna be one of those
princes in name only.
That's why you're
working so hard.
I've finished twice
as much as usual.
So next time they can't
say anything about it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
True.
It's not that I mind
doing paperwork.
Still--
I don't want to lose sight
of what's happening
with the people.
It's vast. My country. And I
want see the entire thing.
I'm not even close yet.
Seeing all of Clarines
would be incredible.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, right! Zen?
What is it?
Do you need a nap?
Yeah, I'm sorry. I'm so tired.
Do you think you could
stay with me while I doze?
Just till Mitsuhide comes?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mh-hm.
That's lovely.
He must've been really tired.
[SHIRAYUKI] Zen works so hard
for someone of his station.
A lot of princes
wouldn't care that much.
I should follow his lead and
get back to work on my goal.
Right, then!
[OBI]
Oh, I see.
The redhead is
apparently familiar
with the dear, sweet Prince.
Heh.
[KIKI]
Zen. It's time to wake up now.
Zen.
Where's Shirayuki?
[KIKI] Mitsuhide took her
home a little while ago.
I see.
Silly girl. I guess
she left this.
[HARUKA]
Greetings, Your Highness.
Please pardon me for
interrupting your rest.
It's nothing. Come in,
Lord Haruka.
[ZEN] You think meeting
with civilians is careless?
[HARUKA] You must remember
the gravity of your position
as the prince.
It is imperative that you
are vigilant about those
with whom you
choose to associate.
I need to protect myself
and preserve my authority.
Trust me. I get it.
[HARUKA]
If you do understand,
then stop inviting commoners
like that strange red-haired
girl into the castle.
[ZEN]
Is she a problem?
She'll have expectations
and take advantage.
What if she asks
to meet the king?
Or tries to exert influence
in royal matters?
And what if this girl
demands special privileges?
She'll use the power of
the crown to further herself,
rather than advancing
by her own strength.
It's unwise to keep
that kind of company.
You stand to gain
nothing from it all
but criticism and
undue conflict.
You believe she wouldn't use
her own strength to advance?
I disagree.
This particular girl isn't the
type to have your expectations.
[grunts]
Your Highness. It's naïve
to think such people exist.
[ZEN] I just wonder if someone
like that would pose a problem.
If someone meets
that description,
please introduce me
so I can eat my words.
Well, you just missed
her, unfortunately.
You were too busy
being judgmental.
[HARUKA]
Uh.
Your Highness!
I didn't come here today to
play ridiculous games with you!
nd yet everything you say
is ridiculous. You may leave.
[grunts]
Very well, then.
I pray you will see the truth
before it's far too late to
rectify the damage. Good day.
Zen.
[ZEN] I need some fresh air.
I'm going for a walk outside.
[HARUKA] That Prince.
I can't believe him.
There's nothing I could say
to change his mind, either.
He's stubborn.
Looks like we have no choice
but to go over his head.
[OBI]
Yes, sir.
Now, then. Time to see
what she's made of.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh.
This herb looks similar
to the shironagi plant,
but the leaves are different.
I should check the encyclopedia.
Oh, no.
I guess I must have left
it back at the castle.
[KAI]
What?!
[SHILA] We can't let
Shirayuki through anymore?
On whose orders?
You must have it wrong.
Shirayuki has permission
to enter any time
as a guest of the prince!
[OBI]
That order's been rescinded.
What? Says who?
[OBI] It's a directive
from the prince himself,
regarding the girl
named Shirayuki:
"In light of the opinions
of my retainers,
this girl shall hereafter
be expressly forbidden
from entering the palace."
No way.
[OBI] Please respect that
this was a difficult decision
for the prince.
Don't make it any
harder for him.
Good day.
[SHILA]
Hey, wait a second!
You should probably tell
the prince something.
We just let Shirayuki through
the gates a few minutes ago.
[OBI]
You what?
It was only a moment
before you arrived, though.
[KAI] She said that she left
a book behind in the castle.
[OBI] I wonder if
she's with the prince.
Did she hear me?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen's being criticized?
And the order that guy gave.
Did Zen really write it?
If I leave today,
I can't come back.
Will I ever be able
to see him again?
Is this the end
of our friendship?
I have to hear him say it.
[SOLDIER B]
You there, stop where you are!
Hm. Interesting hair color.
Are you the girl
they call Shirayuki?
I am.
I thought that's who you were.
I have been informed that
you are a guest of the prince.
Apologies. I didn't
mean to frighten you.
Thanks.
[SOLDIER B]
No problem here. False alarm.
[SHIRAYUKI] I was suspicious
before, but now I'm sure of it.
[SHIRAYUKI] The only reason
I'm allowed anywhere near Zen
is because his power
prevents interference.
[SHIRAYUKI]
That settles it.
I'm going to pass the test
so they'll have no power
to keep us apart.
No matter what they do.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Then no one can stop me.
What? An arrow?
[SHIRAYUKI]
"Red-haired intruder,
you are no longer welcome
as a guest of the prince.
You have been warned.
Leave at once."
This is serious.
Someone really wants
to keep us apart.
But who?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Why would someone in this castle
go to such lengths to prevent
me from seeing him?
It can't be Zen.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I know it.
[SHIRAYUKI] I'm going
to find him. Right now.
[OBI]
What the--?
I don't believe this girl. That
shock didn't scare her away?
[OBI] She sure is taking
the scenic route
to the prince's
quarters, isn't she?
No matter, she's just
making my job a bit easier.
Run along home, little redhead.
[ZEN]
Shirayuki!
I thought you left.
And why are you running?
Zen.
What're you still
doing in the palace?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh.
Oh, um...
I left my book earlier.
Is that all? Then why
be in a hurry?
Are you sure you're
telling me everything?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh. Yes, for the most part.
Oh, interesting.
So. What's the story
with the arrow?
[ZEN] Someone shot at
you inside the castle?
Imbeciles.
Why didn't you alert the
soldiers as soon as it happened?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Sorry. But don't get mad.
Please just hear me out, okay?
How on earth could
I not be angry?
And why are you treating
this like it's no big deal?
It is a big deal.
I was afraid.
And I was angry, too!
Even so, I wanted
to talk to you first.
I won't leave here
without a fight.
If someone wants to keep us
apart, I will confront them.
I'll make them tell
me why to my face.
You mean alone.
If I do it by myself,
they'll probably be
more honest with me.
[ZEN]
You can't.
Zen!
[ZEN] At least that's what
I should say, but I won't.
I'll wait for you. Be careful.
Listen, though.
Please don't do
anything too rash.
If the person you
confront gets out of hand,
use my authority
to make them stop.
And there might
be more than one.
[SHIRAYUKI]
All right.
If I find them, I'll
keep them in my sight.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Do you think you know who it is?
I'm not certain, so I
shouldn't say just yet.
Oh.
[ZEN]
Now you see.
This is how it is. I make
enemies quite easily.
[door opens]
Zen.
Is something the matter?
I need a favor.
[SHIRAYUKI]
There's so much about this place
that I don't understand.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I didn't realize that Zen's mood
could have such an effect on me.
I'll return to my quarters now.
I leave the rest of it to you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Zen's not even certain.
How will I ever figure out
who's behind all of this?
[HARUKA]
What're you doing here?
Do you serve in the court?
No, sir. I'm only visiting.
With whom?
Well, I--
How did you gain
access to the castle?
I entered through
the Poet's Gate.
But I had permission
from somebody.
I'm on my way to see him now.
If you come along, he'll
explain the situation to you.
[HARUKA]
Will he?
It's right this way.
[HARUKA]
Hold it!
[HARUKA] Once I find an
intruder in the castle,
I can't allow them
to go any farther.
I command you to leave
here immediately.
Few hold the power
to welcome outsiders.
If you had clearance
to be here, I'd know.
You don't look like you're
of sufficient social status
to be invited by anyone
with that much authority.
[SHIRAYUKI]
That sounds familiar.
This is the man I'm looking for.
Well, then.
If what you say is the truth,
then that does make me
an intruder in the palace.
Looks like you'll have to
stop me with your sword.
[SHIRAYUKI] I didn't even
have to seek him out.
He came right to me.
[OBI] "This girl shall hereafter
be expressly forbidden
from entering the palace."
[SHIRAYUKI] No, that didn't
sound anything like Zen.
You believe she wouldn't use
her own strength to advance?
I will use this
sword! Stay back!
Use it, then.
And yet everything you say
is ridiculous. You may leave.
[growls]
Would you know
anything about an order
supposedly given by Prince Zen?
[OBI]
Great work.
You aren't the type to be
scared by a little arrow.
What? Who're you?
[OBI chuckles]
[OBI] Don't worry.
I'm harmless now.
I've no chance of escaping,
so I might as well
tell you the truth.
I wrote the order, and I shot
the threatening arrow, too.
He's innocent.
It was all just me.
[HARUKA]
Don't spout such nonsense.
I am the culprit, but I was only
trying to protect the prince.
I would never dare seek
the help of a commoner.
[OBI sighs]
[OBI] Aristocrats have such a
weird sense of pride sometimes.
[ZEN]
You're right about that.
Prince Zen.
Is that the whole truth?
That you did it
for me, Lord Haruka?
Yes, it is true, Your Highness.
Your plan was quite misguided.
[ZEN]
If things hadn't worked out,
it would have made
this place unbearable.
Sir.
You were hiding?
How long did you listen?
I found him just before he
found you, so I heard it all.
It took a lot of self-control
not to jump into the
conversation sooner, you know.
But forgive me
for eavesdropping.
It's all right,
I understand. Zen.
Peasant!
How dare you call His
Highness by his given name!
Down, boy.
She has permission.
You know what?
I think it's important
to have people around
who value hierarchy and
social status above all else.
[ZEN] I lead people who have all
kinds of different perspectives.
I need to understand
their points of view,
no matter how different
they are from mine.
Lord Haruka, do you value
your position in my court?
I do.
Then you should never
abuse the privilege.
You've been warned.
[HARUKA]
Yes, Highness!
[ZEN sighs]
[OBI] Well, I guess
that wraps things up.
[ZEN]
Not so fast.
You can call me Obi, Master.
[ZEN]
I'm not your "Master."
Listen. I'm going to keep a very
close eye on you from now on.
You don't have to worry.
I'm far too afraid of that girl
to mess with her ever again.
Why should I believe
a word you say?
'Cause I'm an honest guy?
And I really like her.
Someone like that could be
a lotta help to a prince.
Right, Little Red?
Well, that seemed excessive.
Kiki, Mitsuhide! Keep this
guy outta trouble!
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes, sir!
You'll be coming
with us, mister.
[OBI]
Ha.
I'd follow you anywhere, ma'am.
Pathetic.
[OBI] I'd prefer you call
me "Obi," my good sir.
[SHIRAYUKI] Who do you
think that guy could be?
[ZEN]
I'm not sure.
But with those two
looking after him,
he shouldn't be
a problem for us.
Don't worry.
This is how it is. I make
enemies quite easily.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I won't.
Zen, look at this.
[ZEN]
An application?
I thought you would like
to know that I'm applying.
[ZEN]
You want to work in the castle?
Yes, as a court herbalist.
It would be great.
I'd be able to walk through
the gates on my own
and officially be on your team.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Besides,
there's someone here I want
to spend more time with.
Maybe one day, I can
be his strength.
I like the sound of that.
Us as a team? That'd be perfect.
[SHIRAYUKI] Moments like
these are what give me hope.
They inspire me to
keep moving forward.
[GARAK]
I am the chief herbalist, Garak.
[ZEN] Your test starts soon.
Think you're ready for it?
[RYU] I know, but I'm only
a kid. It's just weird.
[ZEN]
Great, we're locked in.
[GARAK] Not to mention
helping your resolve.