[KIKI]
We've come quite a long way.
[MITSUHIDE]
Looks like we'll be able to
reach the village by sundown.
[ZEN] Raj's party will
probably reach the castle
around the same time.
[MITSUHIDE]
Right.
Although, it might
take them a bit longer
since they've got the
Claw of the Sea members.
Shirayuki, how are you feeling?
Shirayuki?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh. I'm sorry?
Do we need to stop
so you can rest?
No. I'm feeling great!
How're you?
Used to this, so I'm good.
All right.
I still can't believe
he's Shirayuki's father,
let alone that he's
the chief of the Lions.
[ZEN]
I never even imagined.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I didn't know it, myself.
But he really is my father.
You were just as
surprised, then?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Mm-hm. I had no idea who he was.
Hey, after we get over
the mountain pass ahead,
we'll be there.
You'll see our village soon!
[ZEN]
Got it! Sounds good!
Well... Shall we?
[MAN A]
The Claw of the Sea has fallen!
[MEN]
All right!
[MAN B] That's the real
strength of the Lions!
[CROWD]
Yeah!
Hey. Is it true you
worked with the prince?
Will you tell us more about it?
Sorry, gotta get ready
for the banquet.
[BOYS]
Aw...
Now, then. Make sure you
bring your best wine!
Yes. I know.
Goodness. He's as
excited as a child.
You all are surprising
the customers.
[MITSUHIDE laughs]
By the way. Where's the chief?
And you know, I don't
see Kazuki, either.
They're taking care
of a separate matter.
And don't need
interruptions right now.
[MUKAZE] I guess I should
introduce myself...
I'm the chief of
the Lions. Mukaze.
I'm your father, Shirayuki.
Hard to believe.
It makes me happy that
you're doing well, Father.
[MUKAZE]
Mm...
Uh! Go on, say
something to her.
Oh. All right.
Well, I'm not dead.
I know that's what
you'd been told.
At the time, I honestly thought
it was the best thing for you.
[SHIRAYUKI] Oh. No, I knew
you were actually alive.
Grandma and Grandpa told
me that much, at least.
[MUKAZE] Ah. I didn't realize
you knew the truth.
How did you recognize
me, though?
I've seen you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Well, they told me who you were
when you showed up at the bar
a long time ago. So I peeked.
Uh? You're kidding? I was
trying to be incognito.
Yeah, you're not
good at that.
Well, I should've known.
Your grandparents weren't
exactly the best
at keeping things secret.
Although, I'm surprised
you remembered.
That trip to the bar
was a long time ago.
Well, it's hard to forget.
I was just in awe.
That was the first time
I'd ever seen my father.
[gasps] I see.
What about you?
How did you know who I was?
Oh. My hair gave it away, I bet.
[MUKAZE]
No, it was more than that.
Huh?
So much more.
You look and sound exactly
like your mother.
[gasps]
[CROWD chattering]
[MITSUHIDE] They said
it was in the mountains,
so I wondered what we
were getting in to.
But, I have to admit
I'm pretty shocked;
this village looks
like it's thriving.
[KIKI]
Mitsuhide.
[MITSUHIDE]
Hm?
Thank you. For caring.
[MITSUHIDE gasps]
That's not fair!
[KIKI]
Hm.
You know you have to warn me
if you're about to be honest.
Otherwise, I get too anxious.
Well, if you'd rather, I can
just keep my thoughts to myself.
Uh! No, no. That's
not what I want!
[KIKI]
Oh?
[exhales] Speaking
of something else.
You got any idea where Obi went?
[KIKI] He said he'd take
a look at the surroundings
just in case.
[MITSUHIDE]
Understood.
How awful.
So, you were basically driven
out of your homeland?
Yes. It was hard.
I was a part of the
family of landowners
to the west of here...
My fiancée was, well,
she was your mother.
But anyway, she was about to
be married off to my uncle.
I stole her back, though,
and so they banished us.
I had no idea!
Impressive! Truly.
[laughs] Thank you.
I did have help;
my beloved wife was
no laughing matter.
[ZEN]
What happened after that?
Travel.
Mainly because of my
uncle searching for us.
We didn't think we
could risk stopping
in one place for too long.
So we just kept
running until one day,
the Lions of the Mountain
from back then took us in.
We had you not long after that.
In this village.
I was born here?
That's right.
And that red hair of yours, wow.
Everyone loved it.
I'd never seen your
mother so happy.
But then... we lost her.
I thought...
I thought maybe this
place wasn't the best
to raise a little girl.
I wanted to make sure
that you were safe.
I was terrified that I
would lose you, too.
That's why I took you
to your grandparents
in order to protect
you from this life.
Um. You know...
When Pops was informed that you
had moved out of the country,
he searched all over!
He looked for you!
He was terribly worried.
I thought we could be the
ones to protect you again.
I was hoping to move you
somewhere that the prince
couldn't get to, a place
where you'd finally be safe,
a place where you could
be with your father.
Kazuki.
Pops saved me, and I
genuinely owe him my life.
I just wanted to help.
But instead you were put in
more danger because of me.
I'm sorry!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Still. This village is good.
And full of good people.
I was wondering...
...do you think maybe you'd
want to live with us here?
[SHIRAYUKI]
I don't think so.
[KAZUKI]
What?!
Thank you, though.
I'm sure you both must
understand how I feel.
Yes, this place is wonderful. It
will always be precious to me.
My home is precious,
too. I appreciate it.
But I belong in
Clarines right now.
[MUKAZE]
It'll be okay, kid!
[KAZUKI]
Ah!
I had a feeling
you'd say that...
I just... I hate nobles so much.
I wish they'd all go away!
I don't mean you,
though, Prince Zen.
I'm sorry I hated
you for a while.
I don't remember doing anything
special to make you like me.
I actually don't mind it.
Whatever, I never
said I liked you.
I tolerate you because
of Shirayuki.
[ZEN]
Well, that is unfortunate.
[KAZUKI] Great, now I'm
getting mad again.
[KAZUKI groans]
Let's go. Want to
get some food?
I seriously doubt everyone
else waited for us
before starting the party.
So, shall we join them?
Oh. Wait.
Before that, I wanted to know...
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi!
[SHIRAYUKI panting]
[OBI]
Yes, Miss?
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Obi!
Oh, good, I heard you
were around here.
I'm sorry. My job
was to guard you.
I'm ashamed of
what I let happen.
Please forgive me.
Please.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
No. Don't speak.
Listen, I know you did what
you could. I don't blame you--
I appreciate the sentiment,
but I disagree.
No matter what,
I was supposed to protect you.
[gasps] Sorry. Bet it was
hard to breathe like that.
[SHIRAYUKI]
No, I'm fine.
I'm just trying to understand
if you're saying it doesn't
matter what I think?
[OBI]
I would never say that...
[SHIRAYUKI]
What a relief.
Then...
That should mean the next
time I come to Tanbarun,
you won't mind being
my guard again.
[OBI gasps]
Is that a yes?
You said we could go to
the castle town next time.
Shirayu... Miss!
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'll be counting on you, Obi.
I'll keep that in mind, Miss.
Please stop bowing now.
[CROWD chattering]
Hey! Shirayuki!
Come on, this way!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh. Wait a second!
Sorry! I'm just excited
about finally telling you
a story I know you'll love!
It's basically the tale of
all of Pop's heroic deeds!
[MUKAZE]
Huh?!
Apparently, this is good wine.
We're supposed to have
as much as we like.
And the master?
All right. Who's up
for a little game?
I know!
If I win, I get to share
a room with Miss Kiki--
[BOTH]
No way!
After that,
Pops chased the brute away
and looked at me and said.
"Think of me as your big
brother." And so I did.
Oh, Shirayuki, I wish
you could've been there.
It was so moving! It really was!
[MUKAZE]
Hey.
Evening. So "Father,"
how's Shirayuki doing?
[MUKAZE]
Talking to Kazuki.
Still. That poor girl.
You must be a prince to speak
to an old man like that.
Impertinent, don't you think?
Maybe.
Well.
It's definitely not like a
prince to come pick a fight
in a neighboring
country for a girl,
no matter how pretty
that redhead might be.
For what it's worth,
Highness. I appreciate it.
[ZEN grunts]
I know.
[KAZUKI]
And then Pops won again!
Wait... Where's Pops?
Oh, he left.
What? He left?
I'm so sorry, Shirayuki...
It's all right.
I never thought I'd be able
to hear about this stuff.
It's wonderful!
[KAZUKI laughs]
[ITOYA]
Hey, Kazuki.
Not again, please?
Again. Sorry, but
I need your help.
[KAZUKI] Be right there.
I guess I'm off!
What is wrong
with these people?!
Probably about time
to call it a night.
Then, consider it
a draw this time.
When are you going to bed?
Now sounds perfect.
Do you mind letting Zen know
before you head that way?
We don't want him getting
his feeling hurt.
[KIKI]
Good idea. Ha, ha.
Sure, I don't mind.
[MUKAZE]
I can't help but wonder...
[ZEN]
Hm?
After all, she is my daughter...
Is she in love with you?
Uh! Wait. Why would
you ask me that?!
[MUKAZE] I figured you
would know the answer.
[ZEN]
Yes, but even so.
[MUKAZE]
You're right.
I should probably go
ask someone else...
Stop making fun of me, old man.
[MUKAZE]
Let's try this, then.
How do you feel?
I love her.
I forbid it!
[gasps]
[laughing] I'm kidding you.
I've always wanted to say that.
That was a joke?
It was. A funny joke.
Prince. "In love" is how
young people should be.
[ZEN]
On that note, I'm off to bed.
[MUKAZE]
Goodnight. Don't catch a cold.
[ZEN]
Uh?
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
Uh! Sorry.
What are you doing down there?
Uh! You overheard us
just now, didn't you?
[ZEN whimpers]
[SHIRAYUKI gasping]
You and Kiki are
staying up here.
The rest of us... we'll be
in the rooms downstairs.
Listen. If anything happens,
let me know right away.
Sure. But don't
worry about me.
[gasps]
I can't promise you that.
Goodnight.
[ZEN gasps]
Wait.
Don't go.
Will you...
Will you stay with me?
Just for a little while longer?
Of course.
I will always stay.
If you want.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Good.
[MAN D snoring]
[MITSUHIDE grunting]
Once we get
back to the castle,
we'll have a lot of
paperwork to take care of.
[KIKI]
And expectations.
Is everything all right?
[SHIRAYUKI, ZEN laughing]
[ZEN]
I do not believe you.
[SHIRAYUKI]
It's true!
[ZEN sighs] I wish I'd could've
been there to see that.
[SHIRAYUKI, ZEN laughing]
I should go. I've been
here for too long.
I forget about time
when I'm with you.
[gasps] Zen. That watch?
The one I borrowed from you...
Oh. This watch?
It broke.
I'm so sorry; I should have
held on to it tighter.
No. It's not your fault.
But still...
I've got the watch back.
But far more importantly,
you're with me, too.
What else could I want?
[ZEN] Shirayuki, will you tell
me more about Tanbarun later?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yes.
There's still so much I
want to share with you.
[ZEN]
And I want to hear it.
We'll have all the
time in the world
once we get back to Clarines.
There's something else, though.
Something important I've
been meaning to say to you.
Shirayuki?
[ZEN]
So, this is everything?
[MITSUHIDE]
Yes.
[MUKAZE]
Shirayuki.
Uh. Do you mind if I act
like a father for a second?
No. Go for it.
I'm glad you found a home.
And glad it makes you happy and
that you chose it for yourself.
Oh, I'm just so proud of you!
And I won't cry... So I'm done.
[KAZUKI]
Bye, Shirayuki!
And goodbye to you, Prince Zen!
Goodbye, everyone!
Shirayuki's here?!
[RAJ]
Shirayuki!
Hello, Prince Raj!
[panting]
[MITSUHIDE] I realize this
was the original plan,
but I never imagined
they'd have another ball.
Neither did I, honestly.
I've been surprised at Raj's
behavior at every turn, though.
Don't sound so glad
about it there, Zen.
I get it.
You feel like he's stealing
Shirayuki's smile, don't you?
[ZEN gasps]
[KIKI] In all fairness,
she did look pretty happy.
True. I hate admitting that.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
I'll accompany you,
Miss, if you'd like.
[OBI] The master said
he would hide his rank
so he could attend
the ball, as well.
[SHIRAYUKI] Wow, I can't
tell if that's reassuring
or if it makes me feel
even more nervous.
C'mon. Let's follow 'em!
Or we could not do that?
Eugena!
[RAJ]
What's this? You two.
It looks like you're
up to something again;
is that what's going on here?
No. We, uh...
Please don't start with us.
I know you feel the exact
same way that we do!
You think it'd be
great if Shirayuki
stayed at this castle
forever, too!
I do not.
[BOTH]
Uh?!
[RAJ] A Shirayuki who stayed
with me on purpose?
Heh.
Boring!
[BOTH]
Uh...
[music plays]
It's the song.
[RAJ]
Yes, it is.
I had them play it.
You should have the opportunity
to dance to the song you chose.
Well then, Prince Raj.
Would you like to have a go?
You might not want
to say it like that.
From you, it sounds
like you want to fight.
Does it really?
Oh, we can settle
something now.
What do you think: were we
finally able to become friends?
[gasps] I believe so.
And I'm clearly the one
who got the better deal.
[EUGENA]
They're so strange, aren't they?
I can't believe they think
being apart is better.
I agree. It's a mystery.
One of those too young
to understand things.
[ZEN]
That Raj...
Look at him, acting
like a prince.
Just awful.
A prince acting like a prince.
Shirayuki, when your hair
finally grows out?
Yes?
Come and show it to me?
But without cutting it.
[gasps] How 'bout this.
You come see me in Clarines,
and I'll visit you here.
Because we're friends!
[gasps]
That's a great plan.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Let's see each other again soon.
Thank you, Prince Raj.
[bell tolls]
And just like that,
they're gone.
Yes.
[RAJ]
Sakaki, bow with me, already.
Now, why would I do
that; I bowed earlier.
[RAJ] Why can't you simply
do what I tell you?!
[OBI]
I heard Miss Kiki and Shirayuki
are in the bath next
door to us right now.
[SHIRAYUKI] We haven't
been like this for too long,
way too long! [laughs]
She's too bright!
[OBI] When I'm with you two,
it always ends up like this.