[ZEN] With Shirayuki out of
our sight in Tanbarun,
we were desperate to catch
Kazuki and get some answers.
But fate had other plans.
You're earlier than I expected.
Nice to see you.
Spare me.
There's nothing nice about the
wild-goose chase you took us on.
Although your audacity
is impressive.
Did you actually believe
we wouldn't be able
to track you down again?
Perhaps we should have
kept you on a leash.
Now that you mention it,
I could have used
a leash last night.
If I'd had one, I might
have been able to bring
that little brat Kazuki back
here and save you some work.
Another disappointment.
How did he escape your clutches?
I, uh...
I almost had him, but
then one of his friends
showed up with some
new information.
[ALL gasp]
He knew where she was.
He said Shirayuki
was in Tanbarun,
so they left to go find her.
[MIHAYA grunts]
Did that information include
that she was staying
at the castle?!
I... Yes?
Shirayuki.
Isn't that standard
practice, though?
Kidnapping a princess
guarded by a knight?
You don't understand what kind
of girl you're dealing with.
You do.
Why not come with
us and help out?
I won't help you do anything.
I may have in the past, but
my days as a villain are over.
[sighs] You don't know what fun
you're missing, my friend.
[ITOYA]
Enough, you're wasting time.
We need to head out, now.
Isn't our business here?
No, not anymore.
Shirayuki's in Schenazade
Castle in Tanbarun.
[BOTH]
Uh?!
What? When did that happen?!
Last we heard she
was in Clarines!
[ITOYA]
I don't know all the details.
Well, that's perfect.
Here for nothing.
Don't complain.
If we hurry, we can
make up for lost time.
So, who's this? An informant?
No, I don't think so.
But I bet he'll report
all of this back
to the Clarines princes.
Shall we take him?
[MIHAYA]
Uh!
Now, wait a second. You started
talkin' about your plans
in front of me on your own.
[MIHAYA grunts]
[splash]
And that's pretty much it.
You're lucky I was able to
get away from them at all.
So, it's not just Kazuki.
[MITSUHIDE] It's seems this
goes deeper than we thought,
and there's no way to tell how
much information they have.
[ZEN growls]
Zen.
Ready a soldier to travel
to Tanbarun tonight.
And find Obi.
[KIKI]
Yes, sir.
Wait. Please take
this with you.
For Shirayuki.
Mihaya. Are you able to walk?
Yes, I think.
[ZEN] You're the only one
who's seen their faces.
I need you to come with me.
What?! Do you mean now?
We're going to Tanbarun?
No. We'll be paying
someone a visit, first.
[knocking]
[door opens]
[SERVANT A]
Pardon me, Your Highness?
Sorry to disturb you.
What is it?
[SERVANT A]
Prince Zen.
[IZANA] It's a touch late.
What do you want from me?
Speak.
[RAJ]
It'll change.
It'll never change.
But I believe we can
change all that!
[SAKAKI]
Well, you're up early today.
Did you have trouble sleeping?
Is there something on your mind?
What's bothering you, Highness?
Sakaki. I'd like to
amend today's plans.
It can't be!
I do not believe it!
That's what I heard.
Seriously?
[GUARDS chattering]
There's a buzz in the air.
That so?
[SERVANT D] Please go in, Miss.
The prince awaits you.
Thank you for escorting us.
Look at the size of this place!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Incredible!
[OBI] I admit I'm impressed,
but why have us meet here?
[SHIRAYUKI] Prince Raj? Are you
hiding somewhere in here?
[RAJ]
Look up.
Hello, Shirayuki.
[RONA] Is our big brother really
studying affairs of the state?
[SAKAKI] Where did you
get that information?
[RONA]
Everyone's talking about it.
[EUGENA] I overheard it from
some soldiers earlier today.
[SAKAKI] It's bad manners
to eavesdrop, you know.
[EUGENA]
Uh...
[RONA] Well, is it true,
then, or what?!
Yes. He brought it up
this morning.
He's never expressed any
interest in the subject before.
Why would he just suddenly begin
studying something like that?!
You sure you're
telling us everything?!
Princess, worrying about
what's not your business
will give you
premature wrinkles.
I wonder. Do you think
inviting Shirayuki
was really a step in
the right direction?
I do. Our big brother
has obviously fallen.
He's "fallen"?
Yes!
In love! With Shirayuki!
Is that what you think?
But, wait.
Didn't he deny it
when you asked him?
He dodged the question, but
that hardly means anything.
It's a typical response
from someone who's confused
by new feelings growing
in their heart.
He's never felt this way
about someone before!
Oh, such exciting news!
[EUGENA] Rona, what are
you planning this time?
[RAJ] I have to say,
I'm pleasantly surprised
you were so eager to spend all
day in the library with me.
Please tell me if you get bored.
Sure, but there are so
many interesting books,
it's pretty unlikely.
[OBI] While I'm over here,
dying of ennui.
Although I didn't think
you would like studying.
Are you doing research on
something in particular?
I'm the first prince
of a powerful kingdom!
It's important to be well-versed
in matters of the state!
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
[SAKAKI]
The maid who delivered your tea
said the two of you seemed
to be getting along.
She said if she didn't
know any better,
she might mistake you
for old friends.
[RAJ]
"Old friends"?
Are you going to be all right
at the end of her stay,
when she has to
return to Clarines?
[RAJ]
What?!
[SAKAKI]
Why don't you persuade Shirayuki
to stay in Tanbarun instead?
I'm sure you could.
[RAJ gasps]
Are you trying to kill me?
I'm retiring to bed now.
Goodnight!
[RAJ]
How could he say such a thing?
If he knew how terrifying
that Prince is,
he would never ask me that.
Big brother...
Keep her here. You
can't let her go away.
[SAKAKI] Oh, I guess
you can't sleep there.
Should I show you to
Shirayuki's quarters, instead?
We're simply friends.
You said so yourself earlier!
There are a million other
beds in this castle!
[door slams]
Wow. He's a rather
presumptuous fool.
[OBI]
Another library day?
[MAID A]
Here's your tea, Your Highness.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Thank you very much, Miss.
[RAJ coughs]
[gasps]
[RAJ]
Shirayuki?
Yes?
[RAJ]
Uh...
[SHIRAYUKI]
What's on your mind?
[RAJ] Well, you see. I've given
quite a bit of serious thought
to what you mentioned
the other day,
about the possibility of
changing our relationship.
[SHIRAYUKI]
And?
I'm curious.
How would you classify our
relationship as it stands?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh! Um.
I'm not sure I know
how to answer that.
Yes, I expected
that you wouldn't.
It's all right, I don't
know if I could, either.
I understand.
But I hope that you're glad I'm
prince of Tanbarun at least.
I've tried my best
to earn that much.
Are you? Be honest.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh.
I, uh, well...
I mean... Uh, ah...
[RAJ sighs]
Well. It's fine.
I'm well aware I have a lot
more work to do in that arena.
Well, then. I have to
find out what I lack.
[OBI]
Mm?
[SHIRAYUKI]
We'll see, next time.
[RAJ gasps]
When I come back to visit again.
I can't wait to hear
all of the townspeople
talking about their prince
with pride in their voices.
I know that they will!
[RAJ gasps]
Wait. How do people
talk about me now?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh. Prince Raj.
You hear that?
She's good for him.
[EUGENA]
Yes.
We cannot let her
go back to Clarines.
We have to make him want to
keep her here forever and ever!
[OBI]
I don't think so.
Shirayuki's place isn't here.
You can't have her.
What?
[RAJ]
Is something wrong?
[RONA]
Why not?!
How could she ever want
to be anywhere else?!
Is there something in
Clarines that's better?
Well, is there?!
[RAJ]
You two, again? What is this?
What do you think
you're doing in here?!
Oh! Our brother's
in the library!
Have you developed a sudden
interest in books?
[RAJ] Uh?! Wh-Wh-What do
you mean by "sudden"?
You obviously don't
understand this,
but I had to bring the work
I usually do at night
in my bedroom out
in to the public!
I am entertaining a guest,
so I had to make an exception!
When did you find them?
Just about a minute ago.
They're so sneaky.
I'm surprised you were able to!
They're no match for me.
[RONA]
It can't be!
I shall be unparalleled!
And I shall write books,
that are about, books!
But I shall write
them in secret!
[RONA grunts]
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[OBI gasping]
Oh! I'm so clumsy!
I'm always tripping
over my own feet!
No. It's fine.
Ah!
Thanks for catching me, Obi.
You're welcome. It's my job.
This might prove to be more
difficult than we thought.
Then why don't we just
not do anything instead?
No, this is only the beginning!
Now, pull yourself
together, Eugena!
[BOTH]
Uh?!
I have had enough!
I don't know what kind of
scheme you're cooking up,
but I won't have it!
Go back to your rooms and...
[RONA] We would've gone
without you dragging us!
[RAJ] I don't care!
You deserve this!
Well, they are
certainly precocious.
They're somethin'.
[SAKAKI]
Good morning, Your Highness.
Prince Raj?
Thankfully, they're
spending some time
in the herb garden today.
Oh, is that what they're doing?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Wow, you have the furagi herb!
It usually only grows this
well in the mountains.
Is that where it's found?
Yep. I used to love
going on long walks
to collect this herb
on my days off.
You'd do that alone?
I've heard there's a group
of vigilantes up there.
Apparently, they defend the
people against bandit attacks.
Oh, are you talking about
the soldiers from the castle?
I'm not.
Ah-hem. They aren't
officially sanctioned
by the kingdom of Tanbarun.
I believe they organized
of their own free will.
But they do a good deed,
so we turn a blind eye.
They must have a keen sense
of justice to take on bandits.
[SHIRAYUKI]
I'm amazed those people exist.
You're more knowledgeable
than you let on, Prince Raj.
Oh. Well.
I know a lot more. Wanna hear?
Yes! I'd love to!
The prince has been pampered
and sheltered his entire life.
Because of that he was
on a destructive path.
Shirayuki has certainly suffered
as a result of his mistakes.
That said, she apparently has a
profound impact on Prince Raj.
He's different now.
I always hoped he'd get
the chance to meet someone
who'd have that sort
of effect on him.
There's a mysterious charisma
about that girl.
A kind intensity.
Her manner disarms people.
So what do you say about this?
Think you two could extend
your stay a little longer?
[laughs] I think you'd
better ask her.
Are you feeling tired, Miss?
No, all the things I saw
today were invigorating!
[RAJ] Hm... So, Shirayuki.
Tomorrow, at the ball,
is there any particular type of
music you'd like to dance to?
Uh. Oh.
Well, actually.
I was barely able to finish my
dance training before I left.
[RAJ]
Training?
Yes. If there's a slow
song with a simple beat,
I think I can do that.
You didn't know how to dance?
No. All I could seem to
manage was spinning around
in circles like people
do at town festivals!
I didn't realize.
In that case!
What?
A violin?
[OBI]
Oh.
[violin plays]
[gasps]
Wow, it's perfect!
I think I could dance to this!
I'm glad.
You'll have to remind me.
You are leaving the morning
after the ball, right?
I am.
I'll try not to embarrass
myself dancing,
then, back to Clarines.
I'm so excited.
I can't wait to tell
Prince Zen all about you.
You'll talk about me?
[SHIRAYUKI] Mm-hm. I'll tell
him how different you seem.
How much nicer you are.
Less than two days now.
[gasps]
[SHIRAYUKI]
Obi! You're awake, too?
[OBI] Yeah. So you
couldn't sleep, either?
[SHIRAYUKI]
No. My mind's racing.
I was wondering what Zen
and the others are doing now.
I was actually thinking
about the same thing.
When I'm all alone,
for some reason I start
missing the Master a little.
He hasn't been yelling
at me as much lately.
I don't quite know how
to feel about that.
I bet Zen's missing
you, too, Obi.
You've got it all wrong.
This is the part where you
tell me how much you miss Zen,
not how he misses me.
What?! Oh, really?
That's right.
While you gaze at the stars.
The stars?
But it's late, so I
understand the error.
You should get some sleep.
Yes, you're right.
[OBI chuckles]
I bid you good evening, milady.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Good evening.
Missing Zen?
[OBI]
Well, that was s surprise.
I had no idea she
would be awake, too.
[OBI]
Who am I kidding?
That's not the first
time I've held her.
It didn't mean
anything then, either.
[PIRATE A]
Land ho!
[PIRATE B]
Ha, ha!
It's been a while since
we've seen dry ground!
That guy's been workin'
at the palace?
Too busy to expect what's
about to hit him.
[laughs] This is gonna be fun!
All right!
Make sure you don't
screw this one up!
[UMIHEBI]
Calm down, boys.
[PIRATE C]
Boss.
[UMIHEBI]
Let the kid dream.
This'll be a lot more fun
if he gets his little
heart's hopes up.
Then, we can appear,
crushing him like a bug,
and scrape him off our shoes.
[UMIHEBI]
Understand the plan?
I can't wait to see
the look on his face!
[CROWD chattering]
You want to lure
Shirayuki outside?
Yes, exactly.
We have to figure out
a plan of action
that will get her alone
with our brother somehow.
To do that,
I think we'll have to strike
in a place where
Obi can't get to us.
[EUGENA] Why are you going
to all this trouble?
Because, I am determined to
help Raj find true happiness!
Rona.
[RONA]
Hush.
It's decided. Let's do this!
[EUGENA groaning]
Right now?
[RONA]
I made up a chant.
The ball tonight is
where we'll fight!
[EUGENA]
Wait, who are we fighting?!
What could they be
up to this time?!
I think you need to be
more honest with yourself.
Be honest about what?
Ugh. Can we just have a ball?
[knocking]
[OBI]
I'm coming in.
You should see
the people arriving.
I've never seen so many pretty
dresses in my life, Miss--
Oh, wow.
I mean, my lady.
[OBI] So, this is the result
of having a team of maids
hovering around you all day.
Yes.
I thought I'd be nervous,
but I had no idea!
Well, being a guest of
the prince is a big thing.
Are you all right?
Prince Raj said you
could stay with him
the entire time if you want.
And he'll have a seat for you,
so you can sit if you need to.
Oh, really?
I can't.
If I sit the whole time, then
it will all be for nothing.
That's true.
Right.
If I start acting
like a crazy person,
clear your throat
to let me know.
As you wish, my lady.
I'm here to help you.
[knocking]
[SERVANT E]
Please allow me to enter.
Master Obi.
A letter just arrived for you
from Prince Zen of Clarines.
It's marked as urgent.
From Zen?
[IZANA] People are trying to
kidnap Shirayuki, you say?
I understand your
concern. However,
I cannot allow you to
travel to Tanbarun.
I thought so. I'm going anyway.
I ask your leave, Lord Brother.
Zen, haven't you
heard the old adage
"it's better to ask forgiveness
than permission"?
This isn't a game!
[IZANA] I'm the one who
accepted the invitation,
which took Shirayuki
to Tanbarun.
I will send them word
and address this matter.
[ZEN] That would be nothing
but a waste of time!
Give me leave to go!
Remember, you're a prince.
It's not proper for you to
deal with this situation.
[ZEN growls]
[OBI] You can't go. It's not
safe for you to attend.
Mihaya discovered
new information.
Apparently the boy who was
looking for you has a companion,
and they know you're
here at this castle.
Mihaya said they're
coming for you.
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[ZEN]
I'm going.
You can't stop me.
And someday, I am going
to marry Shirayuki.
[gasps]
Shirayuki!
Found you!
[SHIRAYUKI gasps]
[IZANA]
Interesting.
If you really feel
that way, then go.
However...
If this leads to consequences
which require me to take action
and involve the kingdom in
some large scale conflict,
then do not dare to
ever bring that girl
back to this castle again.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Where am I?
[RAJ]
She was just with me!
Uh! Tell me why!
[UMIHEBI]
I'm so sorry,
but you won't be able
to go back home anymore.
[SHIRAYUKI]
No, Obi, no!