[RYU]
Looks like it stopped raining.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, good.
I should harvest
the roka fruit now,
while the smell isn't as strong.
[RYU] Right. Did you finish
organizing the file on Laxdo?
I did.
I wish I could be there to take
notes on their recovery, though.
I know the feeling. You could
if it weren't so far away.
Yeah, it's too bad.
[door closes]
[ZEN]
I don't know what to do.
She doesn't deserve this.
[OBI]
Master!
No need to fear. Obi's returned!
Obi! You were only supposed
to be gone for two days!
[OBI] Well, I hadn't
been out in a while.
I guess I got carried away.
So, did I miss anything
big while I was gone?
[ZEN] Yes, as a matter
of fact you did.
Uh? What happened?
veryone believes that Zen
and Shirayuki are engaged.
So she's been getting a
lot of unwanted attention.
Some people are sucking
up to her now.
Others are trying to
figure out which houses
have lost favor with me and why.
I told Shirayuki to keep
an eye out, but still.
I hope it's not going to
interfere with her work.
[ZEN]
All right.
Obi, I want you to act as her
bodyguard until further notice.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh.
For real?
You can't be serious, Master!
Did you forget about when I
stalked and threatened her?
[ZEN] It's up to her
to forgive you for that.
I see no reason to hold
it against you, now.
After all, when you left I
thought you might not come back.
But you did.
You've earned my trust.
[RYU] I'll start harvesting
on the west side.
Sounds good.
[KIKI]
Shirayuki.
[OBI chuckles]
Well, I'm surprised to
see you two together.
You shouldn't be!
Kiki and I have been paired
up on watch quite a bit.
We've had fun haven't we, Kiki?
[KIKI]
No comment.
I'm confused.
You mean you already
knew this monkey
was one of Zen's attendants?
[SHIRAYUKI] Uh. Yes,
I did know about that.
The Master was pretty
mad when he found out
we had talked at Laxdo.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Uh...
Zen suggested that Obi
should act as your
bodyguard for a while.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Huh?
Garak agreed to allow
him in the gardens
if it's in your best interest.
As a matter of fact,
she said she would look
aggressively for any way
she could put him to good
use doing the dirty work.
Huh?
[KIKI] He's yours as
long as you need him,
and if you feel like you don't,
you can just send him away.
What? Hey, hold on! Kiki!
[OBI] Oh! Have I even
introduced myself?
I'm Obi, but I've gone by
many different names.
The rest is secret.
Uh, why're you
covering your face?
[SHIRAYUKI]
We're harvesting the roka fruit,
and they give off fumes
that get you drunk
when you breathe them in.
I'll remember that for later.
[SHIRAYUKI]
What are you doing?
[OBI]
I thought I could help out.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Oh, Ryu! This is Obi, and--
[RYU] Yes, I know.
It's fine with me.
As long as the prince and chief
herbalist have agreed to it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
Um. Yes, they have.
[OBI] All right, enough small
talk, let's harvest some fruit!
[SHIRAYUKI] Only pick the ones
that have a four-pointed star
on the end, and stay away
from the shriveled ones,
we can't use them.
[OBI]
Got it.
[SHIRAYUKI]
How do you feel?
[OBI]
What?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Are the fumes affecting you?
[OBI]
I don't think so.
Is this the star shape
you're talking about?
[SHIRAYUKI]
That's it.
[OBI gasps]
What's wrong with you?
[OBI]
Oh! Oh.
Oops. I guess my hand
moved on its own.
[nervous chuckles]
[SHIRAYUKI] Well, make your
hands do something useful
and take these.
[OBI]
Sure thing. I'm sorry.
We're gonna put these bottles
in underground
storage now, right?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Yeah.
The ones they took down there
six months ago should be ready,
so let's check on those
and bring them back up
to the medicine room.
This must be the most
boring job ever.
Oh, no. The longer you do it,
the more interesting it gets.
Really? I guess it does seem
like you're enjoying it so far.
Being an apprentice
court herbalist
and friend of the prince
could have its perks.
Though it's obviously
not all fun and games.
[MITSUHIDE sighs]
That meeting ran long.
Hm? Hey, look.
[ZEN]
Um?
It appears to be going
well down there.
[ZEN]
Yeah.
I've got a question.
Do you sometimes wish
Zen weren't a prince?
Or that you had higher status?
[MITSUHIDE]
Mm!
[ZEN exhales]
[OBI]
Uh?
[SHIRAYUKI]
Give me that.
Uh...
Watch what you say.
Next time I'll take
it as an insult.
[OBI]
Right.
That guy's got it all.
She is somethin' else.
Hey, hold on! Wait for me.
I'm sorry!
[GARAK] This batch's been
fermenting for six months.
You should take a sip so you
know what it tastes like.
Go on, try it.
You, too, Mister...?
I'm Obi!
Try some, Obi.
--[SHIRAYUKI] Burns!
--[OBI] Oh, yeah!
[laughs]
Pardon, Miss Garak.
I believe you gave them the
alcohol instead of the medicine.
Yes, I did!
Nice powers of deduction.
That's why I liked it!
[GARAK, OBI laugh]
[thump]
[RYU]
Uh?
[groans]
[RYU]
Shirayuki!
[OBI]
You all right, Miss?
[GARAK]
Oh, what have I done?
Come on girl, can't
you hold your liquor?
[ZEN exhales]
[OBI] Do you sometimes
wish Zen weren't a prince?
Or that you had higher status?
[IZANA]
Zen!
Prince Zen!
Huh?
[MITSUHIDE grunts]
Uh?
You called for me, Lord Brother?
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh.
[IZANA] I'd like to introduce
you to Mitsuhide Louen,
an Eastern Sereg Knight.
I've hired him to
be your attendant.
I don't need an attendant.
[MITSUHIDE] Prince Zen makes
quite an impression.
[ZEN exhales]
Where're you going?
[ZEN]
For a walk.
[MITSUHIDE]
I'll come, too.
[ZEN]
No, thanks.
Prince Izana gave me
strict instructions
to remain by your
side at all times.
Be honest.
You would have preferred to
work for my brother, right?
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh? That's not true!
Please, I could see it in
your face from the moment
he introduced us.
You obviously respect him more.
[MITSUHIDE]
He's even more observant
than I expected him to be.
I shouldn't have
let my guard down.
[window opens]
[MITSUHIDE] Uh! Prince Zen,
wait! Please come back!
Prince Zen!
[ZEN]
Atri!
It's about time!
You're late again today.
I was beginning to think you
weren't gonna make it at all.
[ZEN] Never underestimate
an escape artist.
[ATRI] But I heard you
had a bodyguard now.
Isn't it harder to get away?
[ZEN] Uh. I'd rather
not talk about that guy.
Why's that? Are you not
getting along with him?
[ZEN] No, I have nothing
against him, personally.
It's just kind of an
awkward situation.
He's been ordered to stay
by me. What do I say to him?
Wow. Must be hard for you.
Princes have it rough.
Why do you act like you
couldn't care less?
No. I do care.
It's just a world that
I don't understand.
I'm nothing but a humble
archer guard, y'know.
You don't understand
'cause you're dumb.
[ATRI] I'm handsome, so
I'm allowed to be dumb.
Plus, I'm a good archer.
[ZEN]
Oh, shut your mouth!
[BOTH grunt]
It's sad that you can't
appreciate my pretty face.
I pity you, Prince.
You're the one who's pitiful.
[ZEN]
Hi-yah!
[ATRI]
Oh, yeah?
[groans]
[laughing]
Very funny.
I'll get you back.
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Zen!
Who's that?
[MITSUHIDE]
Your Highness!
I think your attendant's
looking for you.
[MITSUHIDE]
Where are you?
[ZEN] Yeah. Sorry,
I have to go now.
[ATRI]
I'll stay up here for a bit,
so no one sees me come down.
Don't want people to find
out you're friends with me.
I'm sorry.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh. Prince Zen!
There you are!
[ZEN]
Let's go in.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh. Great!
Your highness, please
wait for me! Prince Zen!
If you don't mind my asking,
are you friends with the boy
who climbed the tree just now?
[ZEN gasps]
You mean, you saw him?
I did.
[ZEN]
He's not my friend.
[MITSUHIDE]
What?
I'm not allowed the
luxury of friends.
Just stay out of it from now on.
I didn't mean to interfere.
And another thing.
You and I aren't friends.
You're only an attendant.
Don't forget that.
Understand?
All due respect...
You don't have to be cruel to
me. I'm still a human being.
[gasps] You mean, I hurt you?
You did. I'm not immune.
[ZEN] Sorry. I just
thought it was obvious.
[MITSUHIDE gasping]
[ZEN]
Forgive me. I meant no harm.
[MITSUHIDE] He was only a
boy, and didn't know better.
Zen bore an immense burden,
but back then I had
no way of knowing.
I would find out soon.
And it would be worse
than I imagined.
[ATRI] So that guy your brother
hired to be your attendant.
His name's Mitsuhide, isn't it?
[ZEN]
Yeah.
[ATRI] The soldiers all seem to
be talking about him these days.
Young guy. Just showed
up out of nowhere.
He's different.
Not like anyone I've ever known,
so I don't know how
to deal with him.
Soldiers and retainers are easy.
But he's straightforward,
which is weird.
[ATRI] I hear the guy knows
how to use a sword, too.
[ZEN growls]
Guessing he always beats you?
Oh, shut up.
You know you can't hide
anything from me, Prince!
I always know exactly
what you're thinking.
[ZEN]
Hm?
Seriously? No one talks
to me like that.
Why? Is that because I'm right?
Wow!
What did you use to
make this sandwich?!
I don't have a clue.
I just snuck into the mess hall
and threw whatever they
had onto some bread.
Is it bad?
No. It's pretty
delicious, really!
[ZEN] You're good at
working with your hands.
[ATRI]
Hm?
Honestly, the time I get
to spend out here with you
is the highlight of
my day. I mean it.
If you've fallen in love with me
I have to say I'm
not interested.
Don't worry about that.
You're not woman enough for me.
[BOTH laugh]
[ATRI]
Prince Zen?
Yeah?
Well, they put me on the
night shift after today.
So I won't be able to see
you in the daytime anymore.
I wanted to ask, though.
Think you'll be able to
sneak out here at night?
What'd I say?
Never underestimate
an escape artist.
[MITSUHIDE] Atri the archer
guard first came to the castle
about four months ago.
He and Prince Zen are
roughly the same age.
They're probably
meeting in secret
because their social status
means they can't be friends.
[MITSUHIDE] The soldiers
tell me Atri's nothing more
than a regular kid who emigrated
here from somewhere far away.
[MITSUHIDE] But something
about him bothers me...
I'm going to look
into this a bit more.
Why are you crouched down in the
middle of the hall like that?
Uh... Oh! Prince Zen!
Hi! How long have you
been watching me?
[ZEN sighs] Long enough
to think you're weird.
I wonder if it's
getting cold at night.
[MITSUHIDE]
Uh. Yes, I believe so.
[ZEN]
You know,
I understand why I can't be
friends with commoners.
I have to protect my
position and authority.
But how am I supposed to know
how close is too close?
My brother does it well.
He strikes a good
balance with everyone.
Maybe I should just copy him.
Then I wouldn't have
to figure it out.
Zen.
[ZEN]
No, stop. Don't say anything.
I'm fine.
It's just something
I've got to work out.
Don't worry about it.
[ZEN] You can go back
now if you want to.
[MITSUHIDE] I think I'll
stay here with you.
[IZANA]
This boy's an archer guard?
You're right. It's not
especially hard for
a foreigner to get a position
like that at the castle.
[MITSUHIDE] Even though he can't
gain access to the interior.
He can still pose a
significant threat
by having minimal
contact with Zen.
[IZANA]
Mm.
I've been able to get more
information on him.
I think the situation here
is a real cause for concern.
I'm glad I assigned a man
like you to this post.
It had been vacant
for quite a while,
but you were definitely
worth waiting for.
I'm honored, your grace.
Zen is rebelling.
He's in a phase where he thinks
he doesn't want to be a prince.
This boy, Atri. You say he
switched to the night shift?
That's what I've been told.
Uh!
[ZEN]
Atri. What--
[gasps]
Prince.
You came.
[ZEN] What happened
to you?! Who did this?!
Glad you could make
it, Your Majesty.
[ZEN groaning]
It wouldn't be wise of
you to run, Prince Zen.
Aren't they cute together.
Hey, what the hell?
Stop messing around.
You didn't have
to do this to me.
Atri?
We couldn't afford to risk
you letting your feelings
get in the way of our cause
this late in the game.
Don't insult me.
I'm the reason we've
gotten this far,
my resolve is as strong
as anyone here!
[gasps]
[MITSUHIDE]
Prince Zen!
[REBELS murmur]
[MITSUHIDE] Your Highness!
What are you miscreants doing?
[REBEL LEADER] You must
be the infamous attendant.
We just need to talk
to Prince Izana.
[MITSUHIDE]
Oh yeah?
You are going to bring
him out here right now.
If you want us to give Prince
Zen back in one piece, that is.
[IZANA] Why don't I
save you boys a step?
[REBEL LEADER]
Uh?!
Izana? But, how?
I bet he knew what was
going on. He's smart.
[ZEN]
Lord Brother.
[IZANA] Tell me who you are
and what it is you want.
[REBEL LEADER]
I refuse to tell you anything
until you lay down
your sword, Izana.
[IZANA]
I asked you a question.
[REBELS murmur]
We are all that remains
of the Lido family
you decimated with your schemes.
[gasps]
[REBEL LEADER]
Prince Izana.
Do you have any idea
how many of the people
who served our family
lost their livelihood
as a direct result
of what you did?
[IZANA] No, I'm not aware
of the exact numbers,
but I do know what kind
of people they were.
Those fools allowed
themselves to be victims,
to be used as pawns in
their lord's machinations.
They stole from good people
to line their own pockets.
[REBEL LEADER]
What did you say?
[IZANA]
I have agents in your country
who care more about your
people than you do.
As we speak,
those forces are winning your
citizens' loyalty for Clarines.
All the while you imbeciles
waste your time.
Your revenge mission
is quite futile.
How dare you?!
Atri! We don't need Zen anymore.
Kill him.
I'll deal with Izana myself.
Watch.
[MITSUHIDE gasps]
[REBELS groan]
[REBELS scream]
[gasps] You're done!
[REBELS yell]
[REBELS groaning]
Atri. Is it true?
You were a Lido rebel all along?
Yes, I was.
Now, all that I have left to
do is eliminate my target.
Tell me why!
[ATRI] I saw it from
the moment I met you.
My people and I were
pathetic by comparison.
[REBEL M yelps]
[ATRI]
You had everything I didn't.
A roof over your head.
All the food you could ever eat.
And the way you smiled at me.
You were born into a life I'd
never know no matter what I did.
It disgusts me that you did
nothing to deserve this.
You took things for granted,
and you'll die for it!
[ZEN whimpers, exhales]
No matter what
you think of me...
...you were my friend.
And that's how I'll
remember you.
[IZANA]
Mitsuhide!
[REBEL N groans]
[MITSUHIDE grunts]
[MITSUHIDE growls]
[ATRI]
Uh!
Someday you'll get yours.
[ZEN]
Atri.
I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
It's for the best.
It... It's so easy
to read your face.
You should really watch that.
And don't let this
get you all sad.
No!
I wonder, Prince, if... if you
hadn't been born into this,
would things have
turned out better?
[ZEN whimpers]
[MITSUHIDE]
He was still so young back then.
Barely more than a child.
Yet he bore a burden which
many adults couldn't carry.
I had no idea how
much he was hurting.
He stifled his cries and
learned to live with his pain.
That kind of burden is the
true birthright of a prince.
[SHIRAYUKI] Zen can't help it
that he's always been a prince
and that some people will always
try to take advantage of it.
[OBI] Master, I never noticed
how beautiful your eyes are.
[KIKI]
Stop it, that laugh is creepy.
[OBI] Boy, is this a
problematic place to spectate.