[USHIMATSU]
Hey!
Thought I'd find
you in here, Hide.
Whoa! Would you look at that!
You've outdone yourself!
Well, I'm not finished yet,
but as soon as we attach the
Golden Dragon and the sculptures
from the wood carving district,
it'll be good to go!
The queen's searching for the
Golden Dragon as we speak, so...
I sure hope she finds it.
I do too.
Oh, yeah.
Got a little
present here for ya.
How incredibly generous!
That's not like you.
[USHIMATSU]
Wha'd'you mean?
Who's being generous?
Come on, go ahead
and take it, would you?
You sure?
Well, thank you.
There are probably others
who deserve it more.
But I'll just accept it
and be grateful.
Hey, you were gonna talk
to the Board of Merchants.
Have you done that?
[USHIMATSU]
Hmm...
[TAKAMIZAWA sighs]
It's no use,
I'm totally stumped.
If we don't hurry, we'll
lose the light completely.
And the forecast said it's
supposed to snow tonight, too.
[KANEDA] You're the one
who made this thing!
How could you forget it?
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Ask Noge!
Come on, are you serious?
It happened almost 30 years ago.
What're you gonna do?
We're looking at a man
who can't crack a code
made by a kid in grade school.
I hope they've found it.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Yeah, but I wouldn't get my
hopes up too high if I were you.
Erika. Feeling any better?
What's the end of the story?
I wanna know.
Wait, what story?
The one you told
me about the girl
that wore a wedding dress
to the crepe cafe.
[laughs]
Oh, that thing.
What'd she say when
she came up to you?
All she wanted was to know if
she could change clothes there,
because she'd just run
away from her own wedding.
Can you believe that?
[ERIKA]
Why?
She apparently changed her mind.
She told me she'd always
wanted to get married,
but then, when the day of
the wedding finally arrived,
it just didn't feel right.
Is the moral of this story
that dreams and
reality are different?
What? Okay,
that's really stupid.
Are you saying it's
the same with Tokyo?
Yeah. Also, it's not
enough just to want it.
You have to have a plan
and resolve to work toward it.
Maybe that's true.
But I'm not gonna
give up my dream
and waste my youth around here!
I might not know what it's
really like, but you know what?
Neither do you, Shi!
You're just out of touch
in whole a different way!
Great, it's snowing.
What are we doing trying
to crack this out in the cold?
We should have figured it out
before we came outside.
[RIRIKO]
Huh... Read vertically.
Vertically?
[RIRIKO]
Here.
[YOSHINO]
"From rabbit, 2,427 step."
What rabbit?
I though we were
in Hippo Park, right?
Hey, wait.
[NOGE]
Huh. Behold, the rabbit!
Oh!
We gotta walk
2,427 steps from here?
But there's no way
that could even be in
the park still, could it?
[ALL]
Hmm...
Two thousand, four hundred
and twenty-seven steps
is easily over a kilometer.
Noge, You said you're sure you
guys buried it in Hippo Park?
Yeah, I feel pretty
certain that's what we did.
I wonder if it's not
buried there anymore.
What? Did someone beat us to it?
In our yearbook,
you specifically wrote
that your big dream was
to be the owner of your
very own book store.
Your wish was granted,
wasn't it?
What are you talking about?
By that logic,
you and Takamizawa
had your wishes
granted, too, in a way.
A champion of justice,
and an F1 racer?
They might've manifested
in different forms,
but they're pretty close.
Wow, I guess that's true,
depending on how you look at it.
Are you saying your
wish really came true?
Heh. Life's complicated,
but I guess from a certain
point of view, it really has.
Maybe the Shining Dragon's
been granting wishes
the whole time it's
been buried there.
Oh...
[SANAE] What is it you wish
to be when you grow up, Anji?
I wanna be a taiko drummer!
Oh, just like
Maki's little brother!
Wow!
[ANJI] And my sister wants
to own a cool clothing store.
She said so in her
yearbook last year.
Whoa, a cool
clothing store, huh?
That's actually a little
surprising, somehow.
Ha! She'd probably
yell at all the customers.
Hey, Noge, I was wondering,
did you inherit your
bookstore from your family?
Nah.
I've just always been
passionate about books.
I went to that bookstore all
the time when I was growing up.
Couldn't stay away.
One day, I heard that
the owner was planning
to close up shop and
move in with his son, so...
...I begged him,
and that's how I ended up
with the house
and the bookstore.
How cool! That's so amazing!
I wanted a store like the one
that always made me
so excited as a kid.
So that's how I've been
trying to run that place.
But it hasn't been easy,
if I'm telling the truth.
The number of children
keeps decreasing every year,
and a little bookstore isn't the
best business plan, anyway.
I'm really only able to sell
a few kinds of things.
Magazines and best sellers.
I wanted people
to read foreign sci-fi,
photography books, crazy
mysteries, and great literature.
But nobody gives
them a second thought.
I like all of those things.
Hearing even one person
say that makes me happy.
It really does.
I wish though.
Well, it seems having
your dream come true
isn't the end all, be all.
Sounds like that's when
the real work begins.
Like when the
heroine of a fairy tale
happily marries the
prince of her dreams,
but we always forget:
The reality is
that living together
as a couple is very challenging.
I think it's important that
you dream bigger, Sanae.
[SHIORI]
So, that's the original code?
[RIRIKO]
Mm-hm.
[SANAE] Hey, is anyone
up for a little wager?
We can place bets on who
will end up cracking the code.
And we'll all buy the
winner whatever they want!
[MAKI]
Ooh, I like it!
[SHIORI]
Erika, what do you think?
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing, I'm fine.
You know, Erika, Anji's been
pretty worried about you.
Isn't it time to think
about going home?
No! I still don't want to.
Why, though?
It's not easy for your mom,
running the restaurant
all by herself.
Are you saying I have
to keep working there
for the rest of my life?
I don't wanna grow old
out in the middle of
nowhere, making curry.
But it's fine to grow
old in the city? Uh!
What's wrong?
I had deja vu
for a second there,
remembering that my mom
told me the exact same thing
when was I having
trouble finding a job.
Now you're the one
handing out the advice.
I'd say that means
you've grown up, Yoshino.
Hey, since it's snowing
pretty hard right now.
Would you mind if
I stayed the night here?
Of course not! Duh!
Why don't you
stay over too, Riichan?
We've got a brand-new sleeping
bag and it's really cool.
Like being a pharaoh--
I'll stay.
[SHIORI]
Good, that settles it, then!
[MAKI]
Wanna see it?
[RIRIKO]
Yeah.
[SHIORI]
Do you mind if I join you?
I don't care.
Do whatever you want.
Yay! That's just what I'll do.
Bit of a squeeze, huh?
[sighs]
That feels good.
They're floating.
Wait, are you showing off?
[SHIORI] I was just thinking
about what you said.
Huh?
That I don't know what
it's like out there, either.
How we're both out
of touch, just differently.
I think you're absolutely
right about all that.
If you don't like Manoyama
and you want to go off to Tokyo,
well then that means
you have a dream
you can shoot for and
I believe that's a lovely thing.
You have something exciting
you can think and plan for.
Which means,
you can take your time.
You don't need to
force it to come true
while you're still so young.
[ERIKA]
I want it to come true now.
But, realistically,
you're still in middle school,
so you can't leave home and go
live all by yourself right now.
Don't you think I know that?
I just can't stand it any more!
In this dumb town, I can't
tell if I'm alive or dead.
I gotta get out of
here as fast as I can!
I'm pretty sure you're not dead.
Erika, sometimes
life's just putting one foot
in front of the other.
Do you know what I mean?
Erika?
Ow!
[SHIORI]
What is it?
Erika?
[ERIKA]
Ow, ow, ow!
Oh, yeah, that's a bummer.
The trauma of becoming an adult.
You've got a baby molar
that wants to come out.
Baby teeth.
Are you supposed to still have
baby teeth in middle school?
Our new teeth always
grow in from the front,
so molars are the last to go.
For most people,
they're usually gone
by the end of grade school,
but some kids Erika's age
still have 'em. No biggie.
You sure know a
lot about this, Maki!
Yeah, well I had a part-time
job as a dental assistant.
No matter how you say it,
what it comes down to
is that Erika is still a kid!
Am not! Erk!
For now you can
take some painkillers
and tomorrow we'll
take you to the dentist.
You can't give her those, Yoshi!
She's not an adult.
People under 15 aren't
supposed to take 'em.
Oh, you're right!
We don't have anything
here that a kid could take.
I guess we'll have
to call Angelica.
No, no!
Please don't tell my mom!
If you do, I'll leave
right now, I swear.
Erika...
Should I buy some, then?
Where, though?
There's literally nothing
open in town at this hour.
Shichan, can you call
and ask Sayuri for advice?
I would, but she just left on
a trip to Okinawa with Kumano.
[SANAE]
At a time like this?
And when did those
two get together?
Maybe Mr. Kadota could help!
Or he could make it a lot worse,
it's so hard to say.
Yeah, I don't think
that's a good idea.
I found it!
Teeth from the bottom
get thrown on the roof,
and teeth on the top,
thrown under the porch!
The teeth actually
have to come out first.
There's a pressure point
that'll relieve the pain.
Oh! I've never heard
about that one!
Hi, do we have
children's pain reliever?
Huh? Children's pain reliever?
There's no way we still have
any of that stuff around.
What in the world do
you need it for anyway?
[YOSHINO]
Okay, little pressure point.
Let's give it a shot!
Hey! Keep your hands off of me!
Come on, hold still, Erika!
If I don't touch you,
I can't cure the pain!
[MAKI]
Okay now, okay.
That tickles!
[MAKI]
Hold still.
[YOSHINO]
Got it!
Sorry, that was the
pressure point for constipation.
[screams]
She said we should
go to the pharmacy
in the shopping district.
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
Don't you think it'll
be closed, though?
[RIRIKO]
That's what I thought,
but Grandma said
she'd call them,
and they'd willing to
open up the store for us.
Is this all you need, hon?
[YOSHINO]
Yes, thanks!
Sorry to bother you so late.
It's no problem.
This is exactly what
the pharmacy is here for.
We appreciate it very much!
Now be careful out there.
[YOSHINO]
Thank you so much for your help!
No thanks are necessary.
You hurry back home and
get her that medicine, okay?
Yep!
[MAKI]
Glad that's done.
Yeah, except
I feel kind of bad now.
I always shop at the
drug store in the supermarket.
I never go to the pharmacy
in the shopping district.
That's understandable.
But you can only get service
like this in local shops.
Wow, this is...
...not even close
to being expired yet.
It looks like they
manage their inventory
really well at that store.
Well, yeah, what did you expect?
Of course, yeah.
You know,
I really love Manoyama.
No matter what people say.
Even if folks continue
to want to leave this place,
and they move off to the city,
and Manoyama empties
out even more.
Even if it keeps getting
smaller and smaller.
I'll never stop loving this
town, and I'll never leave it!
[ringing]
You've reached the dorm.
No, he's not here.
What happened?
Is Anji missing?
[ANGELICA] It's just, Anji
hasn't come back yet.
He's gone!
[police siren]
Anji!
--Anji!
Answer us if you're out here!
Anji!
Hey, no worries. He'll be fine.
So, you're positive
he's not there?
Okay.
Well, if you hear anything.
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
Any sign of him at all?
[YOSHINO]
Uh-uh.
We checked the
shopping district.
But the snow makes
it really hard to see anything.
Still, though, he's just a kid.
There's no way he
could've gotten that far
by now, is there?
Where do we think he would
go in snow like this?
I have a thought!
Maybe the Shining Dragon's
been granting wishes
the whole time it's
been buried there.
[YOSHINO] You don't
think he went looking
for the Golden Dragon?
Maybe he's hoping
it might grant his wish
and bring Erika back home
to him and his mom.
Let's try Hippo Park!
[SANAE]
Anji!
[YOSHINO]
If you're out there, respond!
--Anji!
Hey!
[KANEDA]
Anji!
Look over there!
Not him. That's just a hippo.
[YOSHINO sighs]
What a relief.
[SANAE]
Sorry, that was my fault.
Hello?
[SANDAL]
Hey, Kindaichi!
Could you tell me how
to brew heartleaf tea?
[KANEDA]
Huh?
[SANDAL] Oh, I found Anji
out in the park a bit ago,
so I brought him to
the police box to warm up.
He asked me if I could make
him some hot heartleaf tea.
Anji!
[ANJI]
I'm sorry, Mom.
What a relief.
[SANAE]
Mm.
[ANGELICA]
Erika.
You're really here!
Erika... I...
Please don't leave us.
Ever again.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Come on, talk to him, Erika.
Give him your word
you won't leave again.
You never know.
Your dream just might
come true in Manoyama
without you having to move away.
If you want to own
a clothing store,
that doesn't necessarily
mean you have to go, right?
If you talk to one of the older
owners in the shopping district,
they might let you take over.
That's how I ended up with
my bookstore, you know.
[screams]
Nobody is going
to want to buy cool clothes
in this crappy
little backwards town!
Who's even gonna
notice your cute clothes
when you're walking
around in rice fields?
Cows? Tanukis?
The town isn't even
lit up at night!
It's so dark and empty
it's like it doesn't even exist!
[ANJI]
Okay! Then I'll do it!
Huh?
I'm gonna open up
a clothing store,
and it'll be all for you, Erika!
I'll make it so you won't hate
living in this town anymore.
I'll make it so you'll want
to stay here with us forever!
Anji.
[ANJI]
Please don't go.
I think I get it now.
We adults need
to get our act together.
We need to make this
a town where young people
will want to stay and
really invest their lives.
Well, we should
do something, then.
What?
I'm thinking about the middle
school that closed down.
Did you hear that the Chief
Handywoman is starting up
an acting troupe that
rehearses in the gym.
There are a bunch of
other empty classrooms.
We could use those somehow.
Yeah, we could put together
Noge's jazz and books,
and we could even have
a heartleaf tea cafe!
Haha. I like it except
for the heartleaf part.
What? Why?
It's the most delicious tea!
[TAKAMIZAWA] Also, if I ever
get fired from the bus company,
I'd want to work there.
So it's kinda like
insurance, too.
[NOGE]
Wait, so, now I'm responsible
for your fallback career?
[laughter]
[ANGELICA]
Are you not hungry at all?
I've got some tasty cookies.
[crunch]
[ANGELICA]
What is it?
Tooth came out.
Oh, you'd better go
throw it out the window.
Do I throw it up?
Or at the ground?
Either one works.
Throw it whichever way you like,
but be sure to throw it
as hard as you can.
Apparently Noge
submitted a proposal
to the Board of Education.
He wants to make a book cafe
in one of the school's
old classrooms.
[RIRIKO]
He's really doing it.
[MAKI]
And interest is spreading.
Now, other people are saying
they want to open shops there.
[SANAE] Maybe I'll start
something up, too.
Lunch combo A: beef steak,
combo B: ginger pork.
I recommend the curry.
Erika, you can be
more friendly than that.
After all, they let you
stay in their dorm,
and told you a
bunch of cool stories.
Whatever. They let me stay
there, but their stories?
Totally useless.
Erika, how 'bout we
visit Tokyo together?
Maybe for a long weekend?
Nah. When I go,
I'll go by myself.
But maybe...
...I'll bring you back a gift.
Well, guess there's nothing
new down here today, is there?
But that's what's good about it.
[MAKI] If people want to
do something, like Noge,
they can do it,
and people that don't want
a change can stay as they are.
Because that's a
completely valid option.
I wonder if all that's left
for this old shopping district
is to finish its purpose
and quietly fade away.
Oh, man.
That would be pretty sad,
though, don't you think?
That's it!
I know just what we can do!
Huh? What the heck
is going on here?
These are Hanging Toro
Lanterns I've brought them over,
from Warabiya village.
I went around to
a bunch of houses,
and asked if I could
have their old ones.
See, they're Toro
Lanterns that you hang
from the edge of your roof
at night to let people know
that everything is okay.
No, I know what they are.
But what are you planning
to do with all of these things?
We're going to hang them up
all around the
shopping district.
Then it will still seem
inviting down there
even when the
stores are shuttered.
And, you'll easily
be able to tell
that people still live there!
We had Doku take
a look at the fixtures
and install LEDs in them.
That means there's
no fire risk, now!
[RIRIKO]
Mm.
Well, not bad.
This is really not bad at all.
This brings back memories.
I used to hang out
in Warabiya village a lot
when I was much younger.
Of course! I don't
mind putting it up a bit.
Great idea!
Just one more thing to enjoy!
Thanks! I'm so glad you like it!
[SANAE]
Huh? Noge's not here?
Oh, that's right!
Takamizawa was saying
they were going to dig up
the Shining Dragon,
so he probably went along.
Did they actually
crack the code?
The first two numbers
were two and four,
which you know,
together, reads "west."
We were reading them separately,
but the code was actually
"west 27 steps"!
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Okay. Let's do this.
[KANEDA]
It's just a freakin' toy!
So, I guess it wasn't
a festival treasure.
[TAKAMIZAWA] The queen is
gonna be pretty bummed, huh?
Oh well.
I remember it looking so, like
so much more solid and cool.
Oh, I don't know.
Noge, think we should
try making a wish anyway?
Sure! Why not, right?
Uh?
[YOSHINO]
Hey!
I guess you really can't
wait for someone else
to make your wishes come true.
You've got to do it yourself.
[SANDAL] When I was little,
I wanted to be a firetruck.
Why?
Because they're red.
Next time:
"The Crystal of Melting Snow."