♪
[DOKUSHIMA grunts]
[DOKUSHIMA] Alright,
I think that should do it.
I used my Medusa
Beta Super Glue,
so that thing should
be solid as a rock!
[YOSHINO]
Great, Thank you, Doku!
[cell phone rings]
[YOSHINO gasps]
[DOKUSHIMA]
Hm?
[YOSHINO]
Mm. Excuse me.
Sanae? Yeah, Doku was able
to fix it right up for us!
Huh? Why? What's wrong?
[SANAE]
Yoshino!
[YOSHINO gasps]
What the...?
[MAKI] Someone exceptionally
dirty broke in here last night.
[YOSHINO]
To get outta the rain?
They tracked in a bit more
than rain, wouldn't you say?
Looks like the dragon's emerged
from its pond. Exciting, huh?
[YOSHINO chuckles] You mean
'cause we knocked over that
idol yesterday? Very funny.
Careful. You know if
this was a horror movie,
we'd be totally cursed by now.
The person who says,
"very funny" is always
the first to go.
Nope, nope, shut up.
I bet someone could tell
us all about the old lore,
right Rii- chan ?
Rii- chan told me she
was staying home today.
he said she got all wet
in the rain last night
and caught a cold.
I've got your kangi for you.
You're making too much of this.
It's not a big deal, Grandma.
[CHITOSE] It's important to
treat a cold right away.
Also, you shouldn't exert
yourself just to help
with that matchmaking whatever.
You've never liked being around
other people much anyway, right?
I hope you were able
to sleep well last night!
Yeah, I did, thank you.
The house is really lovely!
Except for those bugs, though.
Ends up, I'm off duty today,
so I get to spend the
entire day with you!
Yeah, well, I'm off duty, too!
You're a competitive eater!
You don't work!
[MAKI gasps] I wonder
if Rii- chan 's okay.
[YOSHINO]
Uh. I bet she's fine,
but I'm checking in on her
this afternoon, anyway.
[KIYOMI]
Wow!
[IZUMI]
I'm so excited!
I've always wanted
to try bouldering!
I had no clue Manoyama
had something like this!
Well, it's outside
of town, though.
This place has even
been used to host
bouldering tournaments before!
[KANEDA] I'll show you
how it's done, Kiyomi.
Here... Then, here.
[gasps]
Hey, you okay?
It's just... I kind of felt
like we were being watched.
[ALL gasp]
So, he's joining us again, huh?
[RIRIKO]
A long time ago, a dragon girl
lived in the town of Manoyama.
The dragon girl
had always been
greatly feared by the villagers.
Why? Because, dragons are
fearsome creatures.
They're different from humans.
You can never tell
what they're thinking.
To keep the dragon
out of the village,
the villagers came together,
and they sang, and danced.
And it worked.
[TOWNSFOLK chatter]
I am a dragon, aren't I?
[TAKAMIZAWA] Looks like the
Chief Handywoman has experience.
Impressive!
She apparently climbed a
bit when she used to have a
job at a gym.
Do any of you happen to know
when this place was built?
[TAKAMIZAWA] The bouldering
walls are pretty new.
But I think this tower has
been here for a long time.
[SANDAL] You can see all
of Manoyama from here.
And the wind feels lovely.
It makes me wonder.
Did the two of them hear
the chirping of the cicadas
and see this
same view, long ago?
Who's that?
I mean my great grandmother
and great grandfather.
So, you're saying
at some point,
your ancestors visited Manoyama?
When he was young, my great
grandfather spent some time
in this area on
a business trip.
That was when he was introduced
to a beautiful young lady
from Manoyama.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SANDAL] Before long, the two
of them fell deeply in love.
They spent many happy days
together here, in Manoyama.
And, eventually, he took her
back to his home country,
where they were married.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Seriously?
Seriously.
That's such a
beautiful story!
So, I guess that
means you must be
a quarter Manoyaman, then, huh?
No, wait, that can't
be right, not a quarter--
One-eighth!
A visitor came here
from a far-off country,
fell in love,
and got married.
That's a perfect story
for our matchmaking tour!
Sure, it's very romantic, but it
kinda defeats your purpose.
He came here, they fell in love,
but then, instead of settling
in Manoyama, they left and
went back to his country.
You're right, though.
If they'd stayed,
it would've been perfect.
We'll promote it in other ways.
[YOSHINO]
Mm. Okay.
[SHIORI] So sorry
to keep you waiting!
We've got French cuisine
for lunch today!
[SHIBUKAWA] Oh, I've never
had French food before.
What? The competitive eater
has never had French food? Ha!
Hey, can you remind me which
fork to use on each course?
[TAIRA] Hm! Only an idiot
doesn't practice before a test.
[KAKIMURA gasps]
What the hell do you think
there is to practice?
Wait.
What is it? Can I help?
Sorry, no. It's just that
I thought you had
another person in your group.
Hey, come on, are you trying
to creep us out or something?
My apologies. But seriously.
I really saw a guy
with big bulging eyes
and a beard with you.
[KAKIMURA] There's nobody
like that on this tour.
Hey, uh, Look at that.
[TAIRA]
Huh?
[KAKIMURA]
[NOGE] Big buggy eyes
and a beard. Am I right?
[ALL gasp]
[TAKAMIZAWA] Yeah, the bento's
not bad at all. Wait a sec.
How the hell did Sandal
get a lunch, too?
Makunochi bento.
A treasure of Japan.
[TAKAMIZAWA grunts] Hey,
where'd the queen disappear to?
[MAKI] Oh, she just went
to check on Rii- chan .
She's endangering herself.
I bet grandma's in rare
form over this whole
matchmaking tour.
Why would the matchmaking
tour upset her?
[TAKAMIZAWA] Oh, you mean
you really don't know?
Hi, can I come in?
Why? What do you want, Queen?
I just came to see how
Rii- chan 's doing.
She's sick so she can't possibly
eat heavy food like that.
So, please go.
[YOSHINO] Could you at
least let me see her!
She should never have been
helping the tourism board
with that matchmaking
tour in the first place!
You silly outsider women
bring us nothing but trouble!
Being an outsider
isn't a bad thing!
We're all just people!
[CHITOSE] Oh, is that so?
Well, I heard that you
broke the dragon god at
Sakura Pond yesterday!
[RIRIKO sighs]
[RIRIKO] I wonder. The dragon,
what did she do after that?
[GROUP chatters]
[YOSHINO] It was no use.
She wouldn't let me see her.
[SANAE]
She really is in a bad mood.
She's holding a grudge because
of the matchmaking? Wow.
What?
We heard about it
from Takamizawa.
Rii- chan 's mother
was an outsider.
She apparently moved
here so she could
marry Rii- chan 's father.
[YOSHINO gasps]
[SANAE] But she couldn't
adjust to life in Manoyama,
so, she left.
I see.
Did you know that, Shiori?
[SHIORI] Mm-hm. Rii- chan has
talked to me about it before.
I guess her mom decided
she didn't want to become
an oribe, after all.
C'mon! Lunch time!
[CHITOSE]
Huh?
[SHIORI]
So, her dad didn't end up
taking over the confectionary.
He followed his wife instead,
leaving Manoyama,
and he got a normal,
white-collar job.
But then, shortly after
Rii- chan was born,
they got a divorce, anyway.
Man. That means from
Chitose's perspective,
her son was tricked,
lured away,
and left brokenhearted
by an outsider.
What happened to her dad?
[SHIORI] He was appointed
to a position overseas
right after the divorce,
so it was decided that
living with Granny Chitose made
the most sense for Rii- chan .
[YOSHINO gasps]
[RIRIKO
"The dragon kept to herself,
staying deep inside the cave,
and eventually, she died alone."
[sighs]
"When the villagers came
to learn of the dragon's death,
they were incredibly sad."
[gasps]
[GROUP chuckles]
[YOSHINO] You think, maybe,
we've done a bad job with this?
No, I don't think so. I mean,
look at how happy the guys
are from the Community Club!
They make really
wonderful souvenirs!
And right now, we've got
a two for one special!
[SANAE] I know this is
a sales opportunity,
but you're single, right?
You sure you don't
want to join the tour?
I'm focusing on honing my craft.
Marriage will have
to come later!
What do you think of
this little guy, Kiyomi?
'Cause if you like it, I'd be
happy to pick it up for you.
h, thanks. But I don't think
my place is big enough for it.
[MAKI gasps]
[SANAE]
Hm? What? What is it?
[KIYOMI gasps]
Look at that.
[KIYOMI]
The dragon?
[KANEDA]
It's just a coincidence, girls!
[RIRIKO]
'Scuse me.
[All]
Huh?
[MAKI]
Hey! Are you feeling better?
[RIRIKO] I went to the library
to read up on the dragon.
[KANEDA]
Can we drop that stuff, please?
I'm afraid you're
scaring the ladies!
But, this--
No "buts", I mean it!
[RIRIKO gasps]
[KANEDA] Come on, you're ruining
the mood in there!
[MAKI]
Hang on!
[KANEDA] Look, you might
like your legends and UMA.
And all that other weird stuff,
but normal girls
aren't like that, okay?
If you're gonna talk to them
about something, keep it fun!
They need to like it here.
[RIRIKO]
Okay, then. Forget it.
[MAKI, SANAE gasp]
Where's she going?
[RIRIKO grunts]
[RIRIKO pants]
[YOSHINO]
Rii- chan !
[RIRIKO gasps]
Hey. You okay?
You've been acting different
since yesterday.
Not since yesterday.
I'm a weird girl.
I've always been a weird girl.
But that isn't-- Okay, yes,
you might be a little weird,
but all of us are,
in different ways,
and that's part of what
makes us who we are!
You mentioned the library
and reading about the dragon.
Did you find out anything?
[RIRIKO gasps]
[YOSHINO]
Hm?
[RIRIKO] There's another
interpretation of the tale
of the dragon. A completely
different interpretation
that everyone here in Manoyama
seems to have forgotten.
The dragons were
extremely wise.
The villagers threw
a party in order
to welcome the dragon girl.
They were hopeful and excited
to learn from her great wisdom.
[RIRIKO]
They thought that a fun,
lively dance would encourage the
dragon and bring her closer.
But, when the dragon girl saw
them dancing around the fire,
she got scared, and she ran
away right then and there.
By the time they realized
their mistake, it was too late.
The dragon girl ended up dying
alone, deep in a dark cave.
And unfortunately,
at that point,
the humans forever lost their
chance to learn from her.
"We created a song to
comfort the poor dragon.
In her solitude, and we sing it
for her with our whole hearts."
Nobody knows the song anymore.
The Manoyama Dance remained,
but the song was
forgotten in no time.
The point is, Manoyama was
originally a place that
accepted and welcomed outsiders.
Rii- chan . That's amazing.
This is really
quite a discovery!
And it's so perfect
for our tour, so...
...let's go and tell
everyone about it!
Come on, you know nobody's
really interested
in that kind of story.
Then, we'll have to
make them interested!
Before the firefly tour,
we'll convince them we're
putting on a little
comedy show
and then hit them with the
dragon story! Good idea, right?
Or, maybe that's a
wee bit too much.
Anyway, we'll figure out
something and it'll be perfect!
How are you able
to smile like that?
Uh...
I can't do that. I can't
be the way you are.
[YOSHINO sighs]
You don't know the
Manoyama Dance,
but you don't even hesitate to
commit yourself to learning it.
You left the countryside
for Tokyo on your own.
You actually worry
about being too normal.
We couldn't be more opposite.
You have all the
things I don't have,
and you can do everything
I can't do! Everything!
I'm so sorry.
[YOSHINO gasps]
[RIRIKO] It's not that I want
to be like you, exactly.
I am who I am.
I want to be that.
But that, must not be enough,
because nobody sees me.
It seems like nobody
understands me!
[YOSHINO] Hm. I don't
think that's true.
I think people here
might understand you
better than you know.
I mean, for instance,
from my point of view,
you're a way more impressive
human being than I am.
[RIRIKO gasps]
You're interested in so
many different things,
and you're not easily swayed
by the people around you.
I wish that was true for me.
Your differences are part of
who you are, and I like them.
Believe me.
You are accepted, and loved.
[RIRIKO]
Why...?
Why are you always so kind?
[SANDAL]
♪ Sleep tonight, go and dream ♪
♪ Feel the comfort of our song ♪
♪ A piece missing, alone ♪
♪ Frightened and seeking home ♪
Wait, is that?
[RIRIKO]
The dragon's song?
♪ all we should have known ♪
[YOSHINO] Sandal, how is it
that you know that song?
It was taught
to me by my mom.
She learned it from her mom,
my grandma, that is,
who learned it from
my great grandma.
[gasps]
[SANDAL] When I was little,
my mother used to sing this song
as a way to comfort me
whenever I cried or was sad.
So, today, I sing
that song for you.
I hope it helped you.
[RIRIKO gasps]
[SANAE] Okay, I think we're
about ready to begin our
Firefly-Filled Evening!
And, thankfully, there's a
zero percent chance of rain.
So we can all relax, and enjoy
those lovely little bugs!
Sure, no problem. Oh, no,
we're all good here.
Okay, see you later!
Yoshi apparently has a
little errand to run,
so she'll have to
catch up with us later.
[RIRIKO gasps]
[YOSHINO]
Here we go.
Mrs. Oribe?
You! Where have you
taken her this time?
If you keep messing
with my granddaughter,
you're going to be
in deep trouble!
I think there's something
you really need to see.
Please, will you come
with me so I can show you?
Give me one good reason why
I should listen to anything
you have to say!
[YOSHINO] Please, ma'am.
Rii- chan will be there, too.
And I can promise. It's Ririko
as you've never seen her.
[GROUP chatters]
Looking at the fireflies will
be a real treat, huh, Kiyomi?
Uh-huh.
So... I was...
I was thinking that maybe
the two of us could, um--
[gasps]
[KANEDA]
What? What is it?
[KIYOMI]
Look, someone's watching us!
[ALL gasp]
Hey, who the hell
are you, weirdo?!
[MASAKI gasps]
Wait, you've got it all wrong!
[KANEDA grunts]
Who are you?
It's Masaki!
[MASAKI grunts]
I'm so sorry, Kiyomi!
I could never convince myself
to give up on the two of us.
I've followed you
this whole time.
[KIYOMI]
I'm so glad it was you, Masaki!
What the--?
Oh god, I think it's her ex.
[GROUP chatters]
[IZUMI] I wonder when they'll
come out. I can't wait!
That thunder caught me
by surprise last night,
and I ended up
falling into the pond!
Oh no, were you okay?
Yeah, I had to take shelter in
this really bizarre building,
like a palace or something,
and I wound up falling
asleep there.
So, the "dragon" who left
the big mess was him.
[KANEDA exhales]
[NOGE]
Aw, c'mon, man, cheer up!
I bet we can make you
forget all about her!
Couple of beers'll do it.
Wonder what's taking
Yoshi so long.
[RIRIKO gasps]
[MAKI]
Mm? There she is.
Sorry to keep you guys waiting!
[RIRIKO gasps]
What's that old bag
doing up here?
[CHITOSE grunts]
[YOSHINO]
Well, here we are folks!
Tonight marks our
last stop on the
Rural Romance in Manoyama tour.
I hope you ladies
had a great time,
because we've
loved hosting you!
I know we only had a
few people participate,
and I know we had our
share of hiccups, too.
But I'm glad to say
I think you got to
experience the real Manoyama.
Also, before we finish,
we need to make a correction.
It concerns the Manoyama Dance.
The one you saw last night.
[USHIMATSU]
Hm?
[YOSHINO] Here's the thing,
the dance had been passed down
as a type of tool to keep
the dragon at bay,
but this was incorrect.
The truth is,
its real purpose was for making
friends with the dragon.
What she say?
As time passed, the original
intent was lost and
it shifted into something
very different. But tonight,
Rii- chan and Sandal have
brought part of it back,
and they'd like to
share it with you.
[ALL gasp]
[USHIMATSU] Hey, Queen, what the
hell are you talking about?
[YOSHINO] Uh. The point is,
this town has a rich history
of being a place that welcomes
and accepts outsiders!
And I believe that's still true
of Manoyama to this day!
[CHITOSE gasps]
[YOSHINO] So, if you've grown
fond of our little town
over the past few days,
and I truly hope
that's the case,
please don't hesitate.
Come back to see us!
We'll be glad to have you
here in Manoyama, any time!
[WOMEN giggle]
[MEN chuckle]
I don't really get it,
but I guess it kind
of worked out, huh?
♪
An old song was forgotten
that went along with the
ancient Manoyaman
tale of the dragon girl.
With your permission,
we'd like to bring it back home.
[SHIORI sighs]
[CHITOSE]
Huh...
[RIRIKO grunts]
This song may have been
forgotten in Manoyama,
but it was kept alive by
someone in another country.
[CHITOSE gasps]
[RIRIKO] I want us to make
it our own again tonight.
So that it may be passed down to
comfort the generations to come.
♪
[RIRIKO]
♪ Sleep tonight, go and dream ♪
♪ Feel the comfort
of our song ♪
♪ A piece missing, alone ♪
♪ Frightened and
seeking home ♪
♪ Please forgive us for all
we should have known ♪
I've heard this song!
I remember it, from when
I was a young boy.
♪ You still can live
here and be free ♪
♪ We all have hearts
pounding strong ♪
♪ Hear the words
of this song ♪
♪ And sleep happily,
knowing you are home. ♪
♪ Sleep tonight,
sleep tonight ♪
♪ So you can dream,
dream peacefully. ♪
[WOMEN]
Thank you for everything!
I'm really sorry for any trouble
I caused you and your group.
Yeah, I'll say you
caused some trouble.
Come visit us again, okay?
[IZUMI] Sure! I'd love
to come back here!
Oh, yeah? Have your
eye on someone, do ya?
Nobody said that.
I hope you two can get back
here for your honeymoon!
[KIYOMI]
Yes! But we--
We have a problem because
Kiyomi's parents have always
been completely against
her marrying me.
All the more reason for you
to come elope in Manoyama!
A town for elopers.
[YOSHINO gasps]
That is such a great idea!
[USHIMATSU] Yeah!
If we welcome elopers
from all over the country,
I'm sure it'll to give
our population a boost!
[SANDAL]
So, the dragon,
surrounded by all of
her friends, finally smiled.
Just a little.
♪
[SANDAL] I sent some manju
to my mom, back home.
She likes chunky azuki bean
paste, but I like it smooth.
Whatcha gonna do?
Next time: "The Dawn Guild."