Please, I beg you!
You have to stop!
Everything I'm doing
is for the town! I swear!
[NOGE] It's not for the town!
You did it for you!
Yep! As only an outsider would!
We will not forgive her!
[YAMADA]
That's right, we won't!
Death by manju!
[ERIKA]
Eat this, you stupid queen!
[YOSHINO]
No!
Could I have some tea?
Please, I really need
some tea now!
What the hell was that about?
[YAE]
Yoshino!
How late are you
planning to sleep?
Get up, already!
'Kay!
[DOKUSHIMA] So, the queen went
back to her hometown, huh?
Yeah, she's taking a
summer vacation, that's all.
Well, you never know,
she might not come back.
Don't be silly!
I'm not; people are
talking about it.
Word is they haven't
seen the other ministers
around town, either.
[SHIORI] That's because
they're all on summer vacation.
Everyone needed a rest
after working on
the Founding Festival.
The Founding Festival, eh?
No vacation could
make up for you having
to take orders from this fool.
[USHIMATSU]
Takes one to know one.
They do deserve a reward!
And Moving Mountains'
ratings are going way up,
but our fight has only
just begun, you know!
Yeah, I'll say it has.
I bet we haven't
even had one percent
of the Manoyama
coupons redeemed yet.
Anyway, here's what you wanted.
Ha! Would you look at that?
I'll use this to perfect
our coming budget
in preparation for the
next Founding Festival!
Should I just forward the bill
for this to the Tourism Board?
Sure. And, I've got
one of these, too.
Come on, you've gotta
be kidding me!
I can't believe you're
using a coupon for this.
[SHIORI] Oh, girls, I wonder
if you really are enjoying
your vacations like you deserve.
[phone ringing]
Hey.
[MAKI] Well, how is it
being back in Tokyo?
Oh, you know, Tokyo's Tokyo.
What's up with you?
Uh, very little.
I called 'cause I literally
have nothing to do.
I thought you said
you were staying over
at your friend's
house right now.
[MAKI] Yeah, they go to work
early, so I'm alone here.
Wanna come stay with me?
At my parents'?
No, thanks.
I have a feeling that
might be a little weird.
Plus, I'm going to see
a friend's play tonight,
and we're going drinking after.
[SANAE] I'm actually going
drinking with friends
tonight, too.
[MAKI] All right!
Look at us, having fun!
[SANAE]
Yeah.
Hey, what's wrong?
I don't know;
just feels weird.
I seriously feel like
an outsider now.
[TAKAMIZAWA] Everything's back
to normal in Manoyama today.
Back to the old
routine already. Gah.
Though, I have to admit,
that TV show's bringing
in more weirdos
than I've ever seen before.
[CHITOSE] Are you helping out
the Tourism Board again?
The queen is on a
little break, isn't she?
There's no need to worry.
I'm not going to try
to stop you.
Nothing Ushimatsu does
ever sticks, anyway.
Things always end up
going back to normal.
I mean, you saw
how it all ended up
at the Founding Festival.
I guess.
But I'm proud of how
hard we all worked on it.
Yay! We can work on this
while Yoshino and the others
are on vacation!
B&amp;Bs?
Right! Mr. Kadota wanted
us to study up on it
for the empty houses in town.
He hopes to be able to work
this into next year's plan.
Once summer break ends,
we can get even more
ideas from the other girls.
Next year, though.
[SHIORI] That's right.
I had forgotten.
The queen's official
term is only one year long.
[YAE]
Oh, these are surprisingly good!
I can send you a ton
when I get back.
We've got plenty of 'em
left over, that's for sure.
So tell me about your job.
Is it going well?
I hope you won't
let your TV appearance
go to your head, now.
Life isn't that simple
most of the time, you know.
Yeah, I know that.
[YAE] Your contract
is one year, right?
What do you plan
to do after that?
I haven't really
thought about it.
[YAE]
Still using that line, huh?
If you're living out
in the country, anyway,
then you might as well
just come home!
Dad knows someone
in a company nearby
who can put in a
good word for you.
It's not a huge
company or anything.
They make kamaboko
and other stuff,
but for Azumigaura,
it's pretty--
What's the matter? Hey!
Young lady, don't you walk
away while I'm talking to you!
I said I'd have lunch
with Saku today,
so I have to go.
Oh, really?
See you later, then.
[SAKUMI] I have to be back
in exactly one hour.
I'm so sorry I don't
have more time!
Government jobs are really
strict about all that stuff.
[YOSHINO] Still in the
Welfare Department?
New Residents Support
Department now.
It's kind of like the rural
revival stuff
you're doing, actually!
Oh, really?
I read all about it online!
You've been working
crazy hard, haven't you?
I don't know.
It's not very going well.
What? You got P'tolemaius
to come out for a show!
Okay, I say that, but I
understand what you mean.
To revive a town,
increasing permanent
resident population
is more important than tourism.
And that's no small
task, am I right?
Right!
Permanent resident population.
[YOSHINO] "In contrast to the
temporary resident population,
which comprises visitors
to a region,
this describes the
number of residents
that have permanently
settled there."
[SAKUMI]
What is it?
Sorry. I had a thought.
I realized I don't count
as a permanent resident
of Azumigaura anymore.
Oh, well.
That's the way it goes.
It's a problem all towns
like ours deal with.
We have some strategies
to assist people
moving back to the
country from the city,
but some people, like you,
take up a new rural residence.
I'd like to bring that up
with my boss, actually.
New rural?
[SAKUMI] Like taking a job
in a small town
that wasn't the one
you grew up in.
From the country,
to the city, to the country.
Wow, I'm pretty impressed, Saku.
You really know your stuff.
[SAKUMI laughs]
Whatever, you're
the queen, here!
What is a B&amp;B?
Making a normal residence
available to the general public
as paid lodging for vacationers.
This could help since
there aren't many places
to stay in Manoyama.
There's a site where
travelers can look
to find houses to stay in.
Manoyama absolutely must
take advantage of this!
Or so Mr. Kadota says.
It's true that if
we'd had more lodging
during the Founding Festival,
people would've been
able to spend more time
exploring the town.
There are plenty
of empty houses.
Yeah.
It'd be so great if we could
take advantage of that!
It's too bad the Tourism
Board can't take charge
of all of them together,
you know?
I wouldn't want to rent
my place out to strangers.
That's true.
I guess it'd be hard to
know who you'd end up with.
Some of the owners probably
won't like that at all.
Okay, tell me this:
What would it take to
make you comfortable
renting out your house
if you were an owner?
Umm, maybe if it's a girl.
Oh, good point.
That makes a lot of sense to me.
And some guests
might prefer staying
in women-only houses.
And they must love UMAs.
[SHIORI] That might prove
a little bit trickier.
[ANGELICA]
Well, personally,
I wouldn't care who it was
as long as they paid me
up front.
[door opens]
[ANGELICA] Hey, this is
a rare sight! Welcome!
Oh, sorry, I'm not
actually here to eat.
Just workin' the beat today.
We've gotten a lot of reports
of suspicious persons.
I get it. There's one
sleeping right over there.
I can't eat another bite.
However, that tuna...
I've got room for that.
[KANEDA] He's not the one
we're looking for right now.
We just got a report that
some people were poking around
an empty house, actually.
An empty house?
How strange--we were just
talking about the vacant homes.
Having lots of empty
houses looks bad
for the town, so, converting
them to B&amp;Bs
would kill two birds
with one stone!
It'd be even better if people
moved into 'em, though.
Especially if some
of those people
could be pretty young ladies.
If they would take up
residence in the empty house
of my heart, forever!
Enough with the poetry.
Back to earth now.
Erika! Shame on you.
Poems provide comfort.
Especially to those
who would otherwise
be crushed by the horrible
reality of their existence!
Oh, gee. Thank you?
I agree with her!
No worries, friend!
[YOSHINO] Huh. I guess the
Azumi Festival is tonight.
[NAGISA]
Hey, sister!
[YOSHINO]
Nagisa!
Where were you headed?
Can you give me a ride?
No, come on.
Riding on the back's illegal.
[NAGISA]
Aww! Gimme a break!
[YOSHINO]
Plus, I can't ride up this slope
with you on the back.
Nah, I think you
underestimate yourself!
I need to get home
and take a long bath.
Then change into my
yukata for tonight!
Oh, you are planning
to go to the festival.
You better!
[sighs]
You sure have it easy, huh?
Not a care in the world.
You seem kinda down.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's just not
very easy to be an adult.
You'll find out soon enough,
whenever you move out.
Man, I just can't wait!
Have you even thought
about what you wanna do
after high school?
Those three years are
gonna fly by, believe me.
I don't care about
moving to Tokyo
or anything like that.
All of my friends are here,
and I really like it.
I don't mind if
nothing ever changes!
But what'll you do about work?
I guess Dad knows
this one company
that makes kamaboko
or something,
so Mom said they could
prob'ly get me a job there.
You know,
like if I wanted 'em to.
Good grief.
I guess Mom really
loves her fish cake.
What's wrong with kamaboko?
I think it'd be
a pretty great job.
I'd be dealing with
locally caught fish
and locally made kamaboko.
Cool!
And after work,
I could hang out with Akkun
and all my friends here.
And eventually I'd marry Akkun
and then we'd both
live happily ever after!
--Who's Akkun?
--[NAGISA] Boyfriend!
Boyfriend?! You little...
[NAGISA laughs]
Still, aren't you
worried your life plan
seems so expected and normal?
Don't you remember what
Dad has always said to us?
"Achieving simple,
normal happiness
is the hardest thing to do."
Oops, I killed the mood.
It's fine!
It doesn't change things.
I still want to do something
that only I can do.
And somewhere other than here!
Oh, Yoshino.
You're always gonna be
the little dreamer
of the family, aren't you?
[KAORU] What? Don't tell me
you still haven't quit, Yuki!
You need to get the hell out
of that company altogether.
Yeah. It's complicated, though.
How's it been having
your own company, Kaoru?
Hmm, we've got plenty
of pitches ready,
but capital is hard to come by.
VCs are hesitant
with young startups.
You've got it nice, Eri.
Living on one of your dad's
properties.
I do still have to pay
rent you know!
Though I guess
it is pretty cheap.
But enough of that.
Let's talk about
something else, huh?
Well, we could always
discuss the new
child-rearing subsidies system.
Why? You're pregnant?
[KAORU] Are you kidding?
No way, not me.
I'm talking about how
businesses are eligible
for these new subsidies
if they hire a mother.
And if you play
your cards right,
it ends up being
a great benefit
for working mothers, too.
It's a total win-win.
How 'bout you, country girl?
Are you planning to
stay out there forever?
I don't know.
My contract's for a year,
so I'll wait and see.
But isn't it boring
out in the country?
It's interesting in its own way,
different from the city.
Hey! I'm actually trying
to get a brand new project
off the ground right now.
Why don't you join me in it?
You could resign from
that "Ministry of IT" thing
way out in the
middle of nowhere.
My project is
much more exciting!
Thanks, Eri.
But believe it or not,
I actually find my current
job pretty interesting.
Plus, it's my duty.
I feel like I want to see this
thing through to the end.
I get it. That's too bad.
All right, then,
I'd be happy to join you!
You should get your
own company sorted first!
You jump at every new thing!
It seems like you've
really changed a lot, Sanae
[SANAE]
Huh?
[YUKI] You're so much more
assertive than you were
when you were here.
You seem more grounded, too.
Well, I don't wanna run
away from anything anymore.
What did you think
about my performance?
[MAKI]
The narrative was weak,
but your performance was
definitely a cut above the rest.
Thank you so much, Maki.
I know you're not someone
who throws out
a compliment easily,
so that means a lot from you!
Thanks, but I'll admit,
I'm more than a little
surprised we ended up
having dinner together.
I totally thought you
invited me to be polite.
No way! Are you kidding?
Don't say crazy
things like that, okay?
Come on, now, I want
you to drink with me.
To us!
So, have you thought
about it more since we talked?
[MAKI]
Hm?
[MOE] I meant...
Are you really done with acting?
Well, I don't know.
Do you know Ryotaro Kurose?
[MAKI]
The film director?
That's right.
He's a fresh up-and-comer.
He's gotten lots
of awards overseas.
He's got this really cool
workshop coming up, see?
What do you think about that?
What do you mean,
what do I think?
He might have his eye open,
looking for new talent
for his next project.
This could seriously be
a big chance!
I guess it could.
[MOE]
You don't need to guess, Maki!
You know that's what
it could very well be!
Come apply with me!
Of course, I know it's an
audition just like any other,
so who knows, right?
Come and apply with you, huh?
[MOE] Do you not want
to do it with me?
Don't tell me you're worried
that you're gonna be
the only one to get cut
or something like that.
It could easily
go the opposite way,
or both of us could
totally get cut.
But you can't know
what'll happen
unless you actually
give it a try!
I don't want you
to give this up!
It seriously breaks my heart.
I just wanna see
you acting again!
Thank you, Moe.
I'll think about it.
Okay, this is yours, then.
That's the end of
all serious-talk.
I swear I'll talk about only
fun things now, okay?
[giggles]
Oh! Get this!
The author of this play
is a huge fan of Sonoda,
the director!
So, he wrote--
[CROWD chattering]
[NAGISA] I think Azumi
Festival is the one thing
that has stayed exactly the same
ever since we were little.
What are you talking about?
Nothing has changed around here.
It's not just the festival!
How can you say that?
That's not true!
For example,
the elementary school
has air conditioning now.
They sure didn't have
that when we were little.
I'll be honest, though.
When we were little,
I did look forward to
the Azumi Festival
every single year.
I'd brag to the kids
in the next town over
about our shrine floats and all.
[NAGISA gasps]
Hey, over here!
I'll see you later, sis!
I'm going to check out
the festival with Akkun!
[YUIKA]
Oh, Yoshino!
I can't believe you're
back in town!
[YOSHINO laughs]
Yuika! Miyako! And Natsuki!
It's been a while!
We've been seeing you online!
You gorgeous queen, you!
Thank you, peasant.
You may approach us.
[MIYAKO]
As you command, my queen!
[BOTH laugh]
How are you guys?
Are you doing well?
[YUIKA] Heh! Believe it or not,
I'm a mom now.
[YOSHINO gasps]
Is it a boy or a girl?
I have twins,
a boy and a girl.
Where are they?
I wanna meet them!
[YUIKA] They're actually at
home tonight with my husband.
Oh, well, that's too bad.
Wait, how come Saku
isn't with you guys?
[MIYAKO] I guess she's
busy running the festival.
I thought she was in
New Residents Support?
Oh, that doesn't
matter for the festival.
They're always shorthanded.
Azumi Matsuri has grown
pretty popular recently.
People even come from
other prefectures.
I guess it does
seem like more people
than there used to be.
Oh, Grandma's here!
I'll see you later!
[YOSHINO]
Okay!
[NATSUKI]
All right!
Time for me to be off
to carry the shrine float!
Nobody's changed, have they?
You should move back, Yoshino!
[SOICHIRO]
Yoshino!
[YOSHINO]
Oh, hi, Dad!
I'm gonna get
going now, I guess.
It was so good to see you!
[YOSHINO]
You, too! Later!
[YAE]
Nagisa isn't with you?
Uh... heh.
Um, she was.
Is she with Akkun now?
Yeah! She is!
So you guys do know about him.
[SOICHIRO laughs]
Well, it's not like they
have a reason to hide it!
My very first date
with your mother
was a night at a festival,
in fact, wasn't it?
That's right!
And I had missed the bus and
was afraid that I'd be too late.
So your grandpa
had to drive me
to my first date
with your father!
But you're not originally
from Azumigaura.
Must have been quite
the drive, huh, Mom?
[YAE]
That's right.
I was raised a lot
closer to the city.
Thought so.
What was it that made
you decide to live here?
What do you mean? Isn't it
obvious? I was here, of course!
Sure, that was part of it!
But I also genuinely thought
that this was a lovely town.
I thought, "I could
live in a place like this!"
[SOICHIRO] I went right for it
and asked her out on a date.
The first thing
I wanted her to see
was this town where I
lived and had built my life.
[YOSHINO]
A place everyone returns to.
A place where people gather.
A place you want
to brag about.
What is it?
It's nothing,
I just thought it was nice.
I'm suddenly really glad
that I came home to visit.
You came back outta nowhere,
and you seemed kind of down.
I wondered what had
happened to bring you home.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I'll make sure that
I can come back
with my head
held high next time.
Maybe it would
be good if I went
to visit you
there sometime first.
In Manoyama?
[SOICHIRO] We all went
there together once
when you were little.
The cherry blossoms were
beautiful there, remember?
Was Nagisa not
born yet at that point?
That's right!
We can bring Nagisa and
Akkun along this time!
Wow! Akkun, too?
What, what?
What're you talking about?
[SOICHIRO]
Well, speak of the devil!
[YOSHINO] Oh, that grilled
squid looks delicious!
[NAGISA]
Want some?
[YOSHINO]
Are you sure?
Okay, yeah!
[SOICHIRO] Yeah, I think
we should take credit
for them being good kids.
Hmm... Not bad, ladies!
Thanks! That means so much!
"Manoyama B&amp;B Proposal."
I feel sure we can
apply with this!
Except it won't
be easy to comply
with all the laws the
hospitality industry has,
you know.
We can do it!
I think we should start by
seeing what kind of shape
the open houses are in!
This one is a little
far from the station,
I know, but it's still pretty
new and in great shape.
If the owner said it was okay,
I think it could work well.
Someone's there.
Is anyone here?
We're just with
the Board of Tourism!
I wonder if this could be what
Kindaichi was talking about.
The prowler sneaking
into empty houses?
[RIRIKO]
Mm-hmm.
[GROUP]
Hola! Hola!
[speaking Spanish]
[Spanish continues]
[SANDAL] The Lamaze
breathing method goes
"hee hee hoo!" Like that.
"Hee hee hoo, hee hee hoo!"
Next time:
"The Queen's Return."