[YOSHINO]
This is... totally crazy!
The Founding Festival is going
to be such a huge success!
We can't just stand around
being happy about it, though.
[YOSHINO]
Huh...?
Uh.
Hello! We're part of the
Founding Festival management.
[SANAE] Are you guys planning
on staying here overnight?
We were going to.
Why, is that a problem?
Oh, no.
You're welcome to
camp, if you want.
It's not like camping was our
first choice or anything,
we just couldn't find any
hotels around here.
We wanted to be first
in line tomorrow
for the exclusive souvenirs.
Why the hell is Ptolemaios
playing a show
out in the middle of
nowhere, anyway?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Also, just so you're aware,
those things show up sometimes.
[CAMPER 13A]
What...?
[SHIORI sighs]
They're right.
Lodging is a bit of
an issue, isn't it?
[YOSHINO] Yeah, if we're
gonna hold an event
that goes beyond Manoyama's
normal capacity,
we've got to think about
that stuff, too.
And there's no way
our public buses
will be able to handle that
extra volume, either.
We've already arranged
for some shuttle buses
to help out with that.
We've got the airport and
train stations covered.
Honestly, there's
nothing to worry about.
You really have
thought of everything.
Thank you.
Hey, is that them?
[KUME]
Welcome! Good morning, everyone!
I'm Kume, and I'm with
Northern Living TV.
--[TOKICHIRO] Hello.
--[HIDEYOSHI] Hey. 'Sup.
[AMAMIYA]
The girls.
Also, may I present
the Revival Gals!
Uh. It's so great to meet you!
I'm the Queen of the Kingdom of
Chupakabura, Yoshino Koharu!
Kinoshta.
Tokichiro.
Hideyoshi.
We really appreciate you
being willing to take
the long trip out here!
Truly a pleasure to meet you.
You, too.
Welcome to Manoyama!
We're thrilled to have
you here, Plus-minus!
[ALL gasp]
[SANAE]
Mr. Kadota.
Okay, then!
How about some food
before rehearsal?
There's a fantastic
eel restaurant nearby!
I could be down with that.
Eel sounds cool to me.
Could I get it Nagoya-style?
Oh, you bet you can!
This way, gents! This way.
Listen, they're called
Ptolemaios, not Plus-minus!
[USHIMATSU]
Yeah, whatever. Let's get going!
[cicadas chirping]
[CROWD chattering]
Chitose. Looks like you
brought a lot of stock.
I've been saying
"Plus-minus, Plus-minus"
nonstop for those TV cameras.
It's only fair I should
profit from it.
Gonna sell a ton of these mats!
Really? You said before you
wanted no part of any of this.
You're one to talk!
You were against these
coupons, weren't you?
Pounce on an opportunity.
That's Business 101.
[ANGELICA sighs]
Looks like we just made it!
Thanks for helping out, Ririko.
Yes, I appreciate it.
Not at all.
Uh? Hey, you've wrapped them
all in sightseeing maps!
[ANGELICA]
That was all Rii- chan 's idea!
Isn't that smart?
She's obviously
my granddaughter.
[MAKI] And that wraps up our
management guidelines.
Next, you'll all head to
your respective stations.
If you're not sure
about something,
please, don't try to guess.
Reach out to HQ instead.
Okay, everyone. Good luck,
and have an awesome day!
[VOLUNTEERS chatter]
[NOGE]
Look at that.
"Chupacabra Kingdom
20th Anniversary
featuring Ptolemaios,
presented by Northern
Living TV right here,
from our town."
This is the real deal.
Come on, man. Why don't
we go find our station.
Oh, all right.
Man, I wish I could
see the concert!
[AMAMIYA] Honestly, how
do you feel right now?
I'm nervous.
I just hope lots of
people actually show up
to the trivia contest.
It's getting to be
about that time, Queen!
Are ya ready to go?
[YOSHINO]
Yeah.
You're fine.
It's going to succeed.
[yawns]
Bound for Sakura Pond,
leaving momentarily.
[CROWD chatters]
Huh?!
[gasping]
[MAKI]
Welcome!
We will now begin the
opening ceremonies
for the Kingdom of
Chupakabura's 20th
Anniversary Founding Festival.
But first, let's have a quick
word from our reigning Queen,
Yoshino Koharu!
Good luck, Queen!
Hold you head up
and shoulders back!
[gasps]
[CROWD chattering]
Here ya go.
Knock it out of the park!
I'm the Queen of Chupakabura,
Yoshino Koharu!
Thank you.
Thank you all for coming
to our festival!
We're so glad you're here.
I'm excited for everyone
to have the chance
to get to know Manoyama!
Welcome! I hope you
have a wonderful day!
[applause]
Right, now, we'd like to
kick off the festivities.
Let's raise the flag and
celebrate with a performance
of the national anthem.
It's an actual country?
I guess that's what
the "founding" refers to.
Manoyama is cracking
me up a little bit!
We've got some time
before the show,
wanna go check things out?
[anthem plays]
♪ As the sun shines
bright and true ♪
♪ And vegetables take root ♪
♪ Downtown there's a view, ♪
♪ rich tradition you see ♪
♪ Sakura pond through... ♪
Yeah, this isn't awkward at all.
[CHITOSE]
Here are your ujikintoki !
Thank you.
And an anmitsu for you,
young lady, correct?
Just a moment, please.
Here it is.
Get your Fortune-Teller Bento
here, ladies and gentlemen!
Find out what kind of
luck you have today!
These are my
Japanese-Style Galettes,
with local buckwheat flour!
If you're tired, just bust
this baby out for a nap!
And it's made with our
locally-grown soft rush!
This looks like a huge success.
Would you care for a snack?
Moth- manju.
[inaudible]
[TECH CREW chattering]
[sighs] What's wrong?
Are they not ready?
They're having trouble
with their equipment
so they pushed back
the start time.
And it's not looking good.
The trivia contest
is about to begin!
If you plan to participate,
please head toward
the enclosure now!
We've got Manoyama
coupons worth 500 yen
for every single
participant here!
[RIRIKO]
Would you like some coupons?
[YOSHINO]
Uh! What? Are you kidding me?
Did they announce it already?
They seem to be in
a rush over there.
Man, we were hoping people
would filter over here
after the show ended.
At this rate, the contest
might completely overlap.
What'll we do?
We've already started
gathering people up, so...
...what can we do?
We'll hold it as planned.
[MAKI]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Let's go ahead and
get things started!
We welcome you...
[BOTH] ...to Manoya-mania
Quiz Extravaganza!
[CROWD cheers]
Wow, I can't believe
what an amazing crowd
we have here today!
Thanks very much! We're so
glad you've joined us!
In order to show
our appreciation,
we're giving you all
coupons worth 500 yen!
Every single one of you!
For those of you that
advance in the game,
we've got even more big prizes!
And for the trivia champion,
it's a trip for two to Guam!
[YOSHINO]
Take me with you!
Okay, it's time for
us to get started!
Why don't you do the
honors, Your Majesty.
Hey, everybody!
Who here wants to go to Guam?
[CROWD cheers]
In that case, here's
your first question!
The Kingdom of Chupakabura
was originally the
Kingdom of Kabura!
Is that true or false?
[YOSHINO]
Aw, that's an easy one!
Oh, there's no rule against
using your phones,
so don't worry about that.
[STAFF 13A]
Attention!
We have an announcement for
those of you who want to see
the special performance
by Ptolemaios.
The show's start was
unfortunately delayed
due to technical issues,
but we're going to begin
in just a moment!
We deeply apologize
for the inconvenience...
Finally! Let's go!
[CROWD chattering]
Hey! Let's go see Ptole.
We don't have tickets.
It's outside, man! We just
need to get close! C'mon!
[SHIORI whimpers]
So, that's a thing that
actually just happened.
It just means you all
won that round by default!
To those that stayed behind:
congratulations!
[laughs nervously]
[rock music plays]
Thanks for coming all the
way out here, you guys!
What prefecture is this, anyway?
It's hot as hell out here!
Are you listening?
Are you listening?!
[CROWD cheers]
I can't hear you at all!
The cicadas are louder
than you guys!
Don't worry about
anything else!
The world revolves around
us in this moment!
The next song we're gonna play
is called "Ptolemaic System."
[music plays]
[MAKI]
Next up, question six!
One of Manoyama's
famous products is kabu ,
which is used as an ingredient
in kabura sushi...
--[distant music, chattering]
--[gasps]
If you think it's true,
please move to the right,
and if you think it's false,
then please move--
What's that?!
We really can't hear you!
Should I raise the
rope yet or not?
Which is it?! Did you say yet?!
[YOSHINO]
I'm sorry!
We'll read the question
again for you.
[KINOSHITA] Who's the
center of your universe?!
This is a hot mess.
[distant music]
[KUMANO]
Crazy. Once the concert started,
people took off so fast.
Of course they did.
We'll just wait and
try to sell them
a few more things
as they head home.
[music plays]
Thanks so much, Manoyama!
We'll see you guys
at Budokan, won't we?
[CROWD cheers]
Here we are!
We've made it to the final round
of the Manoyama Quiz!
Put your hands on those buzzers!
The right answer is worth
a whopping 1,000 points!
Those are high stakes!
Yep, they sure are! Let's do it.
Okay.
"One of Manoyama's most
famous traditional arts is--"
The answer to that one
has gotta be "sculpting"!
I'm not gonna fall
into that trap!
I wasn't finished yet.
Okay.
[chimes]
[ALL]
Hm?
Ping Pong!
Yeah, that's correct.
[CONTESTANTS]
Huh?
"One of Manoyama's most famous
traditional arts is sculpting,
but as a lesser known fact,
which sport experienced an
underground boom here?"
The answer is "table tennis."
Ping Pong!
You've got to be kidding me.
So, we have a winner,
ladies and gentlemen!
The champion of the Manoya-mania
Quiz is contestant 115!
Tell him what he's won!
[YOSHINO]
Congratulations!
It's a vacation for two in Guam!
Uh, tell the folks your name!
My name is Alexandre Cena
Davis Celibidache.
Wow, lovely!
And who will you be taking
along with you on your trip?
Mr. Kindaichi!
Huh?! You mean me?!
Well, no matter who goes,
we hope you'll have a
wonderful time together!
Thank you for playing
our Manoya-mania Quiz!
[applause]
How the heck did Sandal
know the answer to that?
Probably just a coincidence.
We'll make him give it back.
[CAMPER 13A]
That was amazing!
[CAMPER 13B]
Ptolemaios was incredible!
I don't know about
you guys, but to me,
that two-hour wait was
totally worth it.
[CAMPER 13C] Yeah! The
Budokon's gonna be awesome!
Members of the
Board of Merchants,
thank you so much for
everything you've done.
Thank you, Yoshi.
It's obvious you really
worked hard on this.
Yeah, thanks for keeping
the whole thing running!
You're welcome.
I'm just happy it all went well.
We managed to sell
a fair amount.
You all have my thanks.
That's not necessary!
And just so you know, we handed
out over 1,000 coupons,
so the town should still
be bustling for a while!
Hey! We're having an after
party a little bit later.
You're all welcome to come!
Heh. I'll pass, thank you.
Oh, right, okay.
Well, I suppose they deserve
a night to let go a bit.
[USHIMATSU]
Great work, everyone!
Very good job!
Another successful Founding
Festival in the books!
Come on! Now it's your turn
to say something, Queen.
Uh... Sure.
I mean, I know we came
up short in a few places,
so there's room for improvement,
but I believe, overall,
it turned out to be a
pretty successful event.
Are you nuts?!
We got 6,000 people
to visit the Kingdom!
So, we fulfilled our yearly
visitor goal in one single day!
It was an enormous success!
Oh. Great!
All right, tonight we drink!
To us!
[ALL]
[ALL chattering, laughing]
[birds chirping]
[yawns]
I'm so hung over.
[SHIORI]
It's hard to believe
there were so many people
here yesterday, huh?
[SANAE] That's how it
is after a festival.
Next weekend it
what really counts.
[MAKI] Yeah, the coupons will
probably have a delayed effect.
You're right.
Amamiya was talking
about it, too.
Honestly, just you wait
until we finally air it.
The TV program is
still on its way.
That could be a huge deal.
[SANAE]
Oh, oh! It's starting!
[music plays]
[VOICEOVER] Come with us
tonight as we follow five girls
who are fighting together
to revive a rural town.
What kind of miracle
is in store for them?
[SAYURI shrieks]
Shiori's on TV!
Wow, this is incredible, Shiori!
[laughs]
[VOICEOVER] The city of
Manoyama, Population 50,000.
The center of town is
full of shuttered shops.
This place, which grew around a
temple, has lost its vibrancy.
What refreshments will be made
available to our dear guests?
Oh, that's indubitably
too big a job for--
What was that?!
Did you say "indubitably?"
[SHIORI] They didn't have
to put that in there...
No worries, it was cute, relax!
[VOICEOVER]
This town needs saving,
and these five lovely young
ladies have risen to the task.
Yet, each of them is still
dealing with her own problems.
Manoyama is a town
that's fading fast.
But these girls have
a secret plan.
Ptolemaios. A rock band that's
popular with twenty-somethings
and currently
topping the charts.
Uh! It's so great to meet you!
I'm the Queen of the Kingdom of
Chupakabura, Yoshino Koharu!
[VOICEOVER] Watch as these
girls bring this town to life.
Their passion truly
created a miracle.
[ALL]
Uh?
What's he talking about?
It makes it seem as though we
were the ones who invited them.
[ANGELICA]
Oh, is that true?
[TAKAMIZAWA] It's just a teeny
bopper reality show.
Hey, can I use this?
Congrats, you.
That's the first one
we've seen yet.
No way! Are you serious?
Sadly, yes.
So, how are any of us profiting?
They haven't even
shown me once yet.
This is B.S.
[music plays]
[SANAE]
Hey, hold on a second!
We didn't even go
to the concert!
How the heck did they do that?
That's the power of editing.
[AMAMIYA]
Can you tell me, honestly,
what effect your efforts
at rural rejuvenation
have had on the town so far?
Well, I-- Nope!
You'll have to see
at the festival!
[VOICEOVER] The Revival Gal's
fight has only just begun.
They didn't show a single
second of the trivia contest.
[YOSHINO]
This isn't right.
Ah... Trust me, we'll bring
in more viewers this way.
Honestly...
[USHIMATSU]
What's wrong with ya?
Come on!
The show had a ton of viewers,
and you all look like you're
headed to a funeral!
He's right!
Manoyama should be
well-known, now.
The "Mountain Movers"
effect is massive!
At least according to some
other municipal governments.
They did kinda dump on
us a bit, though.
Come on, no one will
be interested in Manoyama
after seeing that. All they
really saw was a live concert
they could've seen anywhere.
The real problem is with the
Manoyama coupons, though.
We handed out over 1,000
of them, and so far,
less than 20 have
even been used.
[YAMADA]
That's it?!
I wonder how many of those
were actually used by people
who made the trip back
out here again.
[YOSHINO]
Is this...?
Is this what we really wanted?
What are you talking
about, Queen?!
Yes, of course it is!
I don't think any of this
is actually helping
the people who live here at all.
The town hasn't changed.
Look around.
Reviving the town
isn't just about
getting people to come here.
We should've learned
at least that by now.
We got so swept up and
excited about Ptolemaios
and the whole "Moving
Mountains" thing.
I don't think I've done any real
good here the last six months.
[SHIORI]
Yoshi...
Hey there, Queen!
Where're you headed?
[YOSHINO]
To the station.
Okay.
[SANDAL] Mr. Kindaichi
said he couldn't go to Guam
because he was
too busy with work.
So, anyone else want
to come with me?
Next time:
"The Queen, Convicted"