Hey, Maki.
How are your rehearsals
for the play coming along?
Oh, going well, I guess.
They're all working really hard.
The singles group didn't
have much else to do.
So they're all
pretty focused.
Aw!
And Riichan's getting used
to singing in front of a crowd.
Isn't that right?
Yeah.
[MAKI]
Oh, Spanish!
One of the Cryptids?
Lucia, was it?
Yes, she's at the
Whitsunday Islands,
in Australia.
Sounds like she's still
traveling all over the place,
isn't she?
It's the middle of summer
down there, too.
While here, the new year
means the darkest depths
of winter for us.
[RIRIKO]
A hitchhiker.
Who'd be out in this snow?
Tokyo might be
a little far for us,
but we'd be happy to
get you to the station.
Erika?!
[ERIKA yelps]
Are you okay?
[YOSHINO] Of the three
festival treasures so far,
we've found the Staff
and the Hanging Drum.
That means one's left.
So we'll be continuing our
search for the Golden Dragon.
Hide, as well as
Tatsuo and Kazushi
from the Woodcarving District,
are all currently hard at
work on the shrine float.
And we've also got the play,
which will reintroduce
the Dragon Song.
We're not just
reviving the festival.
We're reimagining it
and making it brand new.
And that brings us
to why we're here today,
which is in the hopes that you,
the Board of Merchants,
will officially join us
in this effort
and agree to be on the
festival production board.
We want a new festival,
deeply rooted in
Manoyama's history.
We ask:
Would you honor us
with your help?
I don't mind being
asked for help at all.
But I can't help wondering why
a certain old ass isn't here.
Uh... Unfortunately, Mr. Kadota
had a previous engagement.
Huh.
Still, as you say,
this is all for Manoyama.
I don't see any reason to object
to what you have planned.
Wonderful! Thank you!
However, the people you see
in attendance here today
are just a small portion
of the Board of Merchants.
If you want to move forward,
we'll need you to go around
and explain this in
person to the shop owners
that couldn't attend
the meeting.
Yes, of course!
We'll visit each and every shop,
starting tomorrow.
And it's all for Manoyama.
[SANAE] The thing is,
even if we try to visit
each and every shop,
there are some
that are never open,
even in the afternoon.
With them in the picture,
it'll be difficult to get every
shop owner's official "okay."
It'll be fine!
I'm sure they'll understand!
[gasps] And do you
know what else?
Maybe the festival will
change some of that!
Maybe they'll come back!
Maybe they'll decide
to open their doors again!
Sometimes I really do wish
I had your optimism, Yoshi.
We're back!
Hey, Erika.
What is she doing here?
[MAKI] She was hitchhiking,
so we picked her up.
Where was she hitchhiking to?
To Tokyo.
Jeez! Was she running away?
[SHIORI] I'm afraid you'll just
have to go back home for today.
Your mother must be
worried about you.
No way.
I'm not going back home.
You're still in middle school--
what'll you do in Tokyo?
Good point.
Do you have any money?
Yes, I've been saving all
my New Year's gift money.
You really thought ahead, huh?
Do you have a place to stay?
Internet cafes.
No, they wouldn't let a
middle schooler stay there.
Then I'll camp somewhere.
If you sleep outside in Tokyo,
you'll freeze to death!
'Kay, I'll camp
without sleeping, then!
[MAKI]
All right, hang on.
Just have a seat, okay?
Yeah, good.
I mean, I do think
we did the right thing
bringing her here,
but I don't think we're
gonna get very far this way.
Listen, Erika,
today isn't a good day
for running away with all
the snow and everything.
Tell me, what's so bad
about Manoyama, anyway?
Why don't you
tell me why you like
this crappy town so much?
I have a feeling this
will probably seem
like a boring reason to you.
But this town is where
I was born and raised.
My family is here,
and all my good friends.
I guess that's really
why I love it.
Make sense?
I don't care about
all that family stuff.
And I don't have
any good friends.
That's why I'm leaving!
Wait just a sec.
Okay, tell me what
you think about this.
What if, instead of leaving,
you try moving in here
with us for a little while.
Also...
It can be a fact-finding mission
since Sanae, Maki,
and I have all lived in Tokyo.
We can tell you all about
what it's like there, okay?
If you're moving
to a new place,
it wouldn't hurt to get
some information about it
and prepare a little bit
for that move, right?
[door opens]
Welcome, ladies!
Today's specials
are Crystal Fortune
and Plum Crystal Fortune
after-hours drink sets.
Thanks, but we're actually
here to talk to you
about Erika.
[ANGELICA]
Huh?
She was apparently
running away from home,
so we have her at our dorm now.
[ANGELICA gasps]
Evening, Patrasche!
What do you mean, "Patrasche"?
You know what? I'm suddenly
feeling kinda sleepy.
I think I'll take a nap.
[door opens]
She really ran away!
Yes, I know,
she's staying at our dorm.
So did you get into
a fight with your mom?
[ERIKA]
We're always fighting.
Yeah, I guess that's how it is
when you're in middle school.
You trying to sound
like an adult or what?
Actually, I am one.
I can remember desperately
wanting to leave the countryside
back when I was
in middle school, too.
I wasn't brave like you,
so I never tried.
I only dreamed about it.
I never did anything real.
But my little sister
is different.
We're kinda like
polar opposites.
She loves her hometown.
She doesn't care
about the city one bit.
Even though I'm her big sister,
she calls me "little dreamer."
Hey, I'm sorry, is my
chatting keeping you awake?
[ERIKA]
No, it's fine.
All right, I'll be
sleeping in Sanae's room
if you need me.
Get some good rest, 'kay?
G'night, sleep well.
I explained everything
to Angelica as best I could.
It wasn't easy convincing
her not to come over here
and pick up Erika right away.
That's great.
Thanks for doing that.
What's with those bags?
We promised we'd
make sure she still
went to school, at least, so
I brought over her
uniform and textbooks.
Has she gone
to sleep already?
No, but I left the bedroom
because I felt like
I might be keeping her up.
Are you sure she won't leave
in the middle of the night?
Don't worry about it.
I've decided to sleep down here.
Hey, wow,
human home security!
Okay, I'm heading to bed.
We've got an early morning.
Let's sleep in the
same room, Sanae!
We can have pillow talk,
and discuss thoughts
on our meetings with
the shop owners tomorrow!
You don't have a clue what
pillow talk means, do you?
[YOSHINO]
Uhh...
I purposefully
ran away from home,
so why am I going
back to school?
Try not to make
such a scary face.
How about if I tell you
a great story from Tokyo?
This one is from
when I used to work
at this adorable little upscale
crepe shop in Harajuku.
A customer came in,
kind of weird.
That place is the holy
land of getting scouted.
All the girls are completely
done up, super fancy,
and of course trying
way too hard.
But this customer stood out
because she was wearing
a pure white wedding gown.
I remember staring and
wondering about her.
Thinking, "What could've
happened to make her
want to eat crepes
in a wedding dress?"
I kept it simple, though, and
just asked her what she'd like.
And then, the girl
in the wedding dress,
eyes bloodshot,
looked directly at me,
and she said--
We're here!
See you after school.
Hold on!
What did she say to you?
I'll tell you the rest on
the way home this afternoon.
You just make sure
to go to class, okay?
[SANAE] I wonder if Erika will
only end up ditching class
and running away again.
Well, I have a feeling it's
nothing Maki can't handle.
We should try to focus
on visiting the shops!
Let's split them up!
Why don't you take
the shopping district
over in the temple area?
Sound good?
[MINO] Asking people to
join the production board?
Don't you think that's
really something
you should be handling,
Mr. Kadota?
Why should I?
I fully trust the queen.
You need to stop mixing
personal and public affairs.
You've been avoiding
Chitose at all costs.
I don't have any
personal affairs
to mix up with anything!
All I do is public work!
Come on, boss, please!
Would you mind keeping
it down a little?
Oh, no, sorry, it was nothing!
Okay, let me know
about the sponsorship,
and you have all our thanks!
You tell me why you like
this crappy town so much!
[YAMADA]
What's wrong?
You're not your
usual cheerful self.
Oh, no, I'm fine!
No worries!
I'm headed off to the meeting
with the event company!
Hey, Riichan,
have you ever wondered
what it might be like
to travel around
like Lucia and the others?
Maybe, but I know I'd never go.
I bet you kinda wish you
could, though, don't you?
You okay, Shichan? What is it?
Yoshino wanted so badly
to get out of the countryside.
So did Maki.
Sanae wasn't in the countryside,
but she wanted to get away
from her home in Tokyo.
Even your granny
wanted more than anything
to leave Manoyama,
way back when.
But I've never wanted to get
away and leave my hometown.
Not once in my life.
I'm starting to think I'm
the weird one around here.
[SETSUKO]
If Chitose is fine with it,
then I'm on board, too.
If there's anything we can do
to help put it all together,
I hope you'll let us know.
[YOSHINO]
Thank you!
But girls, what you see
is what you get here.
I'm not sure how much help
we'll really be in the long run.
Oh, no!
Please don't worry.
We're glad to have you on!
[YOSHINO]
All right. Next?
That's good.
Have a bite of this, Yoshi.
It's really amazing.
Delicious!
Isn't it?
It's a croquette from
this little butcher shop
over in the temple area.
I've become kind
of addicted lately!
See, it's things like
this that really get
my mind racing.
I believe the shopping
district still has a chance
to make a comeback!
[SHIORI]
We're back!
That was fast.
Is there anything
I can help with?
No, everything is
taken care of here.
I've got to go pick up
Erika pretty soon, though.
Oh, I was hoping
to lend a hand.
Why don't I go for you?
[school bell ringing]
Why didn't Maki
come pick me up?
Sorry, am I
a disappointment?
[ERIKA] I wanted to hear
the rest of the story.
[SHIORI]
What story do you mean?
[ERIKA] Never mind.
I'll ask her when we get back.
So tell me, why did
you suddenly decide
to run away from home?
You've never even thought
about leaving Manoyama
so I doubt you would understand.
Is that what you think?
Maybe you should
give me a chance.
No?
I left 'cause I had a dream.
I was an adult, and I was at
that restaurant, making curry.
That sounds like a lovely dream.
Ugh. Yeah, see, somehow
I knew you wouldn't get it.
That is the last thing
I want to do with my life.
That's why.
Delicious!
Hey, what would you think
of getting out of town?
Leaving and closing up shop?
You want some of this?
Curry is always best
after three days.
I wouldn't need to go
to school. I could work.
I'd do anything to help out.
I don't wanna waste my youth
in this dumb old town!
What are you talking about?
This restaurant is yours.
For goodness' sake,
I named it after the two of you!
I know that!
Why should that matter?
Anji and Erika, I mean,
what the hell's that?
It's stupid!
What do you mean, "it's stupid"?
Look, if you hate being
in the country that much,
you can just go to Tokyo,
or New York,
or Dubai, or wherever else!
Just the thought
of getting old here
in this dried-up town is
enough to make me depressed.
Scares the hell out of me.
It's my worst fear.
Next up, the Tanpopo Cafe.
Oh, this is it.
What the heck?
If you're looking for
the café, it closed last year.
And I'm pretty sure
the hardware store
is actually closed up for
their lunch break right now.
[NOGE] Menial work
is rough, eh, Queen?
Not menial at all!
It's important stuff!
Talking to every
shop owner sounds like
a daunting task.
But it shouldn't be too hard,
they're good people.
Hey, so...
I know it might be nosy
to ask this question.
But why do so many people
maintain their shops here
and then choose to leave
them shuttered so often?
You don't beat
around the bush.
My apologies if the
question was out of line.
The answer is simple.
The people who own those
shops are living comfortably
for the time being.
I see.
But, and hopefully this
doesn't sound rude,
it doesn't look like
they're making money.
Even if their sales
don't support their shops,
they've built up
reserves over the years.
Their children have
grown up and gotten jobs
in the city.
They only need to
support themselves.
They can afford to kick back.
If that's the case,
they should rent them
out to other people.
We have all these shops.
It seems like a
terrible waste for them
to sit empty all the time.
Most of their homes
are on the second floor
of their shops, though.
Understandably they don't
want random people
on their first floor.
I mean, it certainly isn't a
simple problem, to be sure.
These people don't really
want their lives to change,
is the thing.
They tend to want things to go
on exactly as they always have.
Plus, think about it,
even if new stores did
open up in this district,
would you really come shop here?
Yeah, of course I would!
The reason I ask is
are you normally a person
who comes out here to shop?
Yeah, I've shopped here before!
Although, not very often,
I do have to admit.
I bet you usually buy
everything at the supermarket.
Well, yeah, I do.
A lot more often
than not, anyway.
Look, there's no shame in that.
It's exactly what
everybody else does.
That's the future.
The bottom line is,
shopping districts
aren't relevant anymore.
We're happy to continue
looking after Erika
at the dorm for now.
If we force her to go back,
she'll probably just
run away again.
I'm so sorry.
I never would've believed
that she would actually
run away like this.
Is Erika coming back
home or not?
Don't worry about
anything, sweetheart.
I'm sure she'll be back
home with both of us
again before we know it.
She was unfriendly
and she cursed a lot,
but it's kinda boring
here without her.
[KANEDA]
Yeah.
They're already
drinking at this hour?
Both of you guys
off duty today?
Yep, that's right!
Finally got a day off,
but there's really
nothing to do around here.
So we have decided
to have a drink!
Nothing wrong with that!
Sometimes it's nice!
Get away from the wife and kid,
just shoot the breeze.
You two are peas in a pod.
Yeah, we've been friends
since elementary school.
And Noge, too.
Remember how
we'd go exploring?
And that hill behind the pond?
The time we found the
Shining Dragon there?
Those were the days, huh?
Wait, what is
the Shining Dragon?
Oh, nothing important,
just a legendary secret
treasure that grants you
a single wish!
No way, really?
Yeah, there was a rumor
about it at school back then.
It was said that somewhere
near Sakura Pond,
a long-lost, secret
treasure lay hidden.
All we knew was that it was
called the Shining Dragon.
A Shining Dragon
that went missing
somewhere near Sakura Pond.
Could you possibly mean
the Golden Dragon?
[BOTH]
Hm?
[RIRIKO]
This is the Golden Dragon,
one of the festival treasures.
It was used in the old
Mizuchi festival.
[TAKAMIZAWA] Yeah, that
actually looks an awful lot
like the one we found.
Don't you think?
[KANEDA]
Yep, that's it.
The Golden Dragon.
Was that the treasure
that was attached
to the roof of the
old shrine float?
Yeah.
Someone supposedly pulled
it off before it all sank
into the pond, but it seems to
have gone missing after that.
So Kindaichi and
the others found it
while they were out exploring
when they were really little?
I guess, and if that's true,
then what is the location
of the Shining Dragon now?
They told us they buried it
in Hippo Park, near the school.
[SANAE]
They buried it? Why?
If you'd like
the short answer,
it was because the Shining
Dragon only grants one wish.
They argued about
what to wish for,
but in the end, they couldn't
pick just one thing.
So, they decided to bury
it until they could all agree
on a single wish.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
I'm closing up now, okay?
[KANEDA, NOGE]
Okay.
Guys, this is a very
important secret, you got it?
Swear not to tell anyone!
This is the secret
code that shows exactly
where it's buried.
Nobody gets it all for himself!
[NOGE]
See?
Now there's no way it can be
found unless all three of us
are together!
How stupid.
I mean, there's obviously
no way that thing grants wishes.
Well, they can't really help it.
They're boys, after all.
I got in touch with Noge,
and he said he'd be
happy to go dig
where they buried the dragon,
but I honestly doubt he's gonna
find anything down there.
Hey, Erika?
What would you wish?
I think if I could have
one wish right now...
I would want to be left alone.
Erika, wait.
Don't try to force
her to talk to you.
It won't work.
Yeah, but...
So how's everything
going with you guys?
Do you think the folks
in the shopping district
are gonna help us out?
Some shop owners weren't around,
but we got okays from
the people we did talk to.
It feels like we're
getting super close
to reviving the festival!
I just hope it does
something to help revive
the shopping district, too!
Right, Yoshino?
Huh?
Hey, are you okay?
You were so upbeat
all afternoon.
I guess.
I'm not really sure
anymore though.
About what?
I talked to Noge today.
All about the shopping district.
He said everyone is comfortable
the way things are.
And then an outsider
like me comes along.
What right do I have to say,
"let's bring this
place to life!"
Maybe we're being
way too pushy with this,
trying to encourage people
who aren't at all interested
in changing things.
It's exactly like the
people in Warabiya Village.
They're just trying their
best to continue on,
keeping their lives the same.
Well, I'm not going to pretend
that what you're saying
doesn't make any sense.
I keep thinking about it.
One thing Noge said was
that shopping districts
aren't relevant anymore.
[SHIORI] Who is he
to decide that, anyway?
You can't just say
they're not relevant!
I was born in this little town.
I've lived here
for my entire life,
and I'm never, ever going
to give up on loving this place!
We understand, Shiori.
It was Noge who said it.
Right, I'm sorry.
No worries.
No, I'm sorry, Shiori.
It's not right for
the queen to be
such a big fat pessimist, is it?
If they're not relevant anymore,
then we'll find a way.
We can make them relevant again!
Agreed. I believe putting
our heads together
will make all the difference!
[phone ringing]
Hang on a sec.
Oh, it's from Takamizawa.
He said they're digging up
the Golden Dragon!
Hey, Takamizawa!
You guys are late, Queen.
Where's the Golden Dragon?
We're about to start digging.
But first, we're gonna
have to figure out this code.
Huh?
What am I looking at?
[RIRIKO]
"The Incantation of Rebirth."
[SANDAL]
I've been to Harajuku before.
I was actually scouted
by an agency,
but unfortunately,
I failed the interview.
Next time:
"The New Moon Luminarie."