♪
[inhales]
'kay.
[SANAE] I can't believe
it's next month.
[SHIORI] It's going to be the
biggest event Manoyama's had
in the past couple years!
The Founding Festival!
It's really the culmination
of all our revival efforts!
So, let's make sure
it's a success!
[ALL]
Yeah!
♪
'Morning, chupa.
Chupa?
[USHIMATSU] We've got an
important visitor, Kabura.
[KUME]
Good to see you all again!
It's me, Kume, from Northern
Living network.
[YOSHINO] You're from the
Regional Mascot Contest!
We really appreciate
you hosting it.
[KUME]
Our pleasure!
You gave quite an entertaining
performance, Queen!
Yeah, sorry about that,
It was maybe a bit too
outta control, there.
Ah, we loved it!
And we've kept an eye
on you since then.
Ah, forgive me, my friend here
is one of the top directors at
our network, and he's
also a Manoyama native!
My name's Amamiya. I heard
that a girl around my age
was working hard to
revitalize the town.
Honestly, it really inspired me.
Well, they were mostly
my ideas, chupa.
Are you familiar with a program
called, "Moving Mountains"?
[SHIORI] My mom and I watch
it together every week!
[KUME laughs]
Thanks for that!
It's called "Moving Mountains?"
Yeah, a reality show that
focuses on exceptional locals.
It's mysteriously very popular.
I actually had to re-write
the proposal several times
before they'd accept it.
[YAMADA]
"The Revival Gals'
One Hundred and Fifty Day
Fight to Save a Town".
This is great!
A hundred and fifty days?
[AMAMIYA] That's how long
you've been on the throne here.
We'll be focusing
on the five of you.
So, we'll be following
you around town,
shooting your daily struggle,
preparing for the festival!
You mean, all the time?
Oh my gosh! We're gonna
be on Moving Mountains?
Filming should be no problem
at all, right, Queen?
Oh, no way!
I actually can't wait!
That's excellent.
Let's give Manoyama
something to talk about!
Cool!
Great!
Is it just me, or is
this pretty crazy?
Alright! Let's get 6,000
people there, chupa!
Six thousand attendees?
That's how many people visited
the palace all last year!
That means, if we hit
that number in one day,
we'll be legends!
No worries! I know that
we can make it happen!
Hey, good morning, everyone! Uh!
I forgot, we're starting today.
Oh! Sorry, I talked
about filming!
Honestly, there's nothing
we can't do in editing,
So, just try to relax.
[SHIORI] Ahem! We're holding
the meeting now, Queen!
Shiori, what're you...?
[YOSHINO] As you know,
the Somen Mega Expo
was pretty specific
to Manoyama.
But for this festival,
we can probably expect
some gatecrashers.
Er, just people.
I mean, we can expect guests
from neighboring towns.
I, too concur with
that assessment.
What refreshments will be made
available to our dear guests?
Oh, that's indubitably
too big a job for--
[gasps]
Yes, that's right. That's why
we... we really must have the
Board of Merchants' cooperation,
but we still haven't
heard back from them.
How does this issue
align with our
current service
level agreements?
I don't-- Uh...
[MAKI] You guys are in
selfie mode right now.
Just try to forget about
the cameras, okay?
Basically, we need to
divide up the work, right?
So let's start divvying it up.
It'd be great if you'd
take that off now.
[RIRIKO]
Understood.
[MAKI] We'll be holding the big
trivia contest in this area.
I see, so, what you're saying
is the stage will, in effect,
be the backdrop?
Yes, exactly. This ensures
people can move---
[ALL]
Hm?
If you truly believe,
your dreams can live.
Dreams really do come true!
Also, if you build it,
then they will come.
[SANDAL] I came. I saw.
I Costner-ed.
[AMAMIYA sighs] Honestly,
I have no words, now.
He's fine, it's all fine.
[AMAMIYA]
So, I heard a little rumor.
Is it true you were working as
an actress back in Tokyo?
Well, I wasn't
exactly "working".
[AMAMIYA] How'd you get involved
with the revival effort?
Oh, it just kind of happened.
[MALE ASSISTANT A]
'Scuse me...
Where should I park
the generator truck?
Behind the palace is probably
the best, thank you!
To tell the truth, my life
had kinda hit a dead end.
I thought I might
see things clearly
if I went back home again.
But for now, I'm realizing how
much fun it can be to work
toward a common goal with
people I really respect.
[AMAMIYA] So you're in
charge of PR, Ms. Kouzuki?
That's right. I used to work
as a web designer in Tokyo,
so, you know.
[AMAMIYA] Honestly, it seems
like it would be hard
to make the decision
to move out here.
Oh, it wasn't
that hard for me.
Out here, you don't have to
deal with crowded trains
or buses, the rent's cheap,
and you're surrounded
by lovely nature. Huh?
[AMAMIYA]
Pause. Hold for nature.
[SANAE]
Uh...
[SANAE] Every day, I feel
like I have a purpose.
I mean, I know that Manoyama
may be a small market,
but that just makes it
easier to see the results
of any effort you make.
It's incredibly humbling
and rewarding to be able to
use my skills to help
revive the town!
[SHIORI]
No good.
What? Why?
We've already used 200,000
yen of our PR budget
on posters and fliers.
Don't you remember when I asked
you to think of something
that wouldn't cost
any more money?
I felt sure that was a joke.
Our Minister of Mediation
is pretty strict!
Don't forget, we can make
that much in a sec
selling our yummy manju.
Come on, what do you say?
Order a box of our
Chupakabura Manju Deluxe!
If those things would sell,
we wouldn't have this problem!
[AMAMIYA] Managing a budget,
that's honestly really tough.
And we're getting
subsidies from the city,
so we can't go
over budget at all.
I see. What's your opinion
about the Queen, Ms. Koharu?
Oh, she's wonderful. She has
an amazing imagination,
and she's great at just jumping
in and getting things done.
Great, can you
tell me truthfully:
what are your current goals?
Your goals for the upcoming
Founding Festival, I mean.
Yeah, sure!
I want our guests to
fall completely in love
with Manoyama.
I want the event to be
chock full of hometown love!
[NOGE] Whoa! "Moving Mountains"
is really here!
I certainly never would have
thought they'd come to Manoyama!
I wonder if our shop
will be on TV?
They want the Board
to set up food stalls?
This area, between the
gate and the palace.
That'll get the most
foot traffic, I think.
Really, I couldn't
care less about
celebrating that silly
Kingdom's anniversary.
[AMAMIYA grunts]
[CHITOSE] It's fine that they're
asking us to set up food,
but if the place ends up being
empty, that would be a disaster.
No, it's okay. People will
come to this. Probably.
And how do you know that?
Everyone is working so
hard to support Manoyama.
Case in point,
I'll help with the food.
Okay, then.
I'll talk things over with
the Board of Merchants.
Thanks, Grandma.
Young man, I want you to
make sure to use that part.
[AMAMIYA] Do you think it's fair
to say that the Queen's passion
for rural rejuvenation
was what ultimately led
you join the team here?
You're wro-- right.
Tell me honestly, Ms. Oribe,
how do you feel
about the Queen?
Well, she always seems
to understand me,
so I like her pretty well.
I understand your role here
is the Minister of Puma.
Do you particularly like pumas?
No, I'm Minister of UMA, or uma,
which is not the
same as puma at all.
It's a term created by
a Japanese person.
What they're actually
called is "cryptids"
and they're fascinating.
I'm currently studying
the Mothman.
His composition's linked
to the digestive system of
both humans and insects,
which suggests--
[YOSHINO] I propose a toast.
To our great work today!
[ALL]
Here you go, girls!
Manoyama's official new
specialty, the Happy Somen!
I apologize for the wait.
No worries! Thank you, Erika.
We're truly pleased to
have you back, as always.
Hold the phone. Are you
wearing make-up tonight?
[ERIKA] Why don't I get that
out of the way for you, sir?
Hey, no one said
I was done, though!
[BOTH giggle]
Is there a problem
or something, Amamiya?
Go ahead and stop recording.
The truth is, I've just been
trying to figure out how
I can frame the queen.
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
The others have all had a touch
of drama to their stories,
you know? But so far,
it feels like you don't really
have anything like that.
[YOSHINO gasps]
[AMAMIYA] You failed to
find work out of college
and were crowned due
to mistaken identity.
It works as an initial hook,
but honestly,
I want an element that will
move our viewers a little more.
Move them how, exactly?
Yeah, it just feels a
little too "normal".
Could you please not
call me "normal", okay?
[SHIORI exhales]
[KUME] How's it going?
Is it good? The footage?
Thank you for the tea.
Yeah, I was able to get most of
the comment sections shot.
[KUME] Well, good for you,
but everyone is a little bit
worried that it might not
be that entertaining.
They shouldn't be.
Honestly, I have a secret plan.
[SHIORI]
Yoshi.
[YOSHINO]
Hm.
I wish he hadn't said that
to you. There are plenty
of ways that you aren't
normal at all, really!
Yeah. Hm?
He was being provocative.
It's all for TV ratings.
Maybe I am just normal, though.
I had hoped that being
made Queen here
could maybe change that. But it
feels like I'm the only one
who hasn't really grown at all.
That's not true!
If anything, you're just a late
bloomer, that's all it is!
I know all of us have
definitely been influenced
by you to some degree.
Yeah, a bit.
Yes, I second that.
Thanks, you guys.
[ALL chuckle]
So, what were you
doing in here, anyway?
Do you mean you
really don't know?
That little girl
right there is Yoshi!
[SANAE]
What? Really?
[RIRIKO] The 10,000th visitor
to the Kingdom of Chupakabura.
[SANAE] Well, that's some
real life drama!
Why haven't you said anything?
Amamiya is going to
cry tears of joy!
Oh, you think so?
Yeah, and I bet you Mr. Kadota
would go straight up
bonkers over it, too.
[RIRIKO] The Queen of destiny,
chosen by the heavens! Chupa!
The legends were all
totally true! Kabura!
He'll be a pain,
let's keep it a secret.
[YOSHINO]
Mm. Agreed.
I have some bad news. We were
only able to raise 30 percent
of our sponsorship goal.
At this rate, we'll be forced
to reduce the scale of the
trivia contest, for sure.
We can't! That's the biggest
draw of the whole festival!
[RIRIKO] We could get rid of
the grand prize trip to Guam.
If we do that, we won't get
any guests from outside of town!
Our first goal has to
be getting them here.
And then, once they're here,
we'll give them a bunch of
coupons so they'll stay.
And so they'll come back.
That's the ultimate goal.
[YOSHINO]
Hm.
It's good that you're trying to
extend the value of the event,
but how do you plan on
covering that in the budget?
I think it might be a
little too much to ask
of the Board of Merchants.
There's no way that old hag
would listen to us, anyway.
We can't ask them
for any more.
Then there's the issue
with traffic management.
We've hired some part-timers,
but it's not enough.
So, what should we do, now?
[door clatters]
[AMAMIYA]\
Excuse me.
I did it! I honestly did it!
Brace yourselves:
Ptolemaios has just agreed
to play at the
Founding Festival!
[ALL]
Huh?
You mean the Ptolemaios?
[YAMADA]
You're kidding!
Wow!
Ptolemaios. He advocated
for Geocentrism...
[MAKI]
No, Rii- chan , not Ptolemy,
What's that?
Talkin' bout Tally-who?
It's a band called Ptolemaios!
They've just had
their big break!
Tickets to their shows
sell out instantly!
[MINO]
My wife's a huge fan of theirs.
[MAKI] Hey, it's the soda
commercial that Moe's in!
[YAMADA]
That's right!
Their song's in the
swimsuit version!
You mean it? Those guys
are really coming here?
They are. I used some
connections I made
back in my old
college media club.
That led me to their
managers in Tokyo.
--[ALL gasp]
--[SHIORI] So cool!
Seriously, this is
pretty amazing.
I'm sure they wouldn't
normally do an event
in the middle of nowhere, right?
This concert alone will
probably draw people
here from the entire country.
Ha! You very much remind me
of my young self, you know.
I like you a lot, chupa.
But there's no way we could
possibly have the budget
for such a famous act!
Nothing to worry about.
It's all taken care of.
My boss has agreed to make it
an official corporate event
for our network.
It will be an excellent
opportunity for us, also.
[YOSHINO] Okay, so, just to
clarify, does that mean
that Northern Living will
be covering the costs?
Correct, that burden
is not on you and now
we can openly promote
the Founding Festival.
Honestly, it kills two
birds with one stone.
It's amazing.
That's free publicity!
Everyone involved
will benefit from this.
It's a genuine win-win!
Oh, but we had planned
to hold the trivia contest
in that big area right
in front of the palace.
You can go on ahead with
whatever you have planned.
We'll handle the show
from here on out.
Right now, we intend to use
that area down by the pond.
You sure that'll work okay?
Won't there be
problems with sound?
"Are you sure?", "But, this,"
"Are you sure?", "But, that."
[ALL]
Huh?
[AMAMIYA] Quitters are forever
coming up with excuses.
That's why Manoyama will
always be a middle-of-nowhere
Podunk town! This is
a huge chance for you!
What could possibly
make you hesitate?
Honestly, nothing!
[YOSHINO, SHIORI gasp]
[AMAMIYA] I'm sorry. Let's just
tackle this head-on, okay?
Head-on.
At least we know he's
a little bit passionate
about the project.
Well, the show is called
"Moving Mountains".
Okay, let's check in with
our guy in the field!
Apparently he's got a pretty
big announcement for us!
Let's give him a call! Amamiya!
Hello! I'm here, back in
my hometown of Manoyama,
visiting the Kingdom
of Chupakabura!
Pretty chill, huh?
Just a palace, no big deal!
[KUME laughs]
He's actually not
too bad, really.
And here are the members
of the wonderful
Manoyama Tourism Board.
Hi there, ladies!
Hi! Great to be here!
[KUME] Oh! Might those five
lovely young women be...?
That's right!
Those in the know, know!
They're the Manoyama
Revival Gals!
Honestly, aren't they so lovely?
[GIRLS chuckle]
Well then, the Kingdom's
Founding Festival,
being held on August 27th,
is right around the corner,
and as a very special guest,
they've got none other than--
A frozen mammoth is coming!
[YOSHINO]
Get off!
[AMAMIYA] Actually, there's no
mammoth, frozen or totherwise.
But! The famous rock band
Ptolemaios will be playing!
[KUME]
Wow! That is a surprise!
[AMAMIYA] More details as soon
as we have them! Stay tuned!
Take it away, Gals!
Come on down, chupa!
[GIRLS]
To Manoyama, kabura!
[SANAE sighs]
Jeez, that totally
wiped me out.
Well, this was our first time
on a national live broadcast!
So we're "Revival Gals", huh?
Oh, man,
they're already posting.
I don't like these
people's tone.
Isn't it good that they're
talking about it, though?
But what's with this
"gals" thing? Can we not?
I guess Amamiya can be a little
on the heavy-handed side, huh?
Yeah, there's no
doubt about that.
But at least he is passionate
about improving Manoyama.
And we do have our goal
of 6,000 attendees.
I can put up with him if
he brings in more people.
And I support any
decisions you make, Yoshi.
Thanks.
I think we need to do whatever
we can to make the concert work.
So, in that case, with regards
to the trivia contest budget,
It might be time to bring
out the battering ram.
Sounds pretty intense.
We'll smash it head-on!
[YOSHINO] To the Board of
Merchants, the Community Club,
and all other attending groups,
thank you very much
for taking the time to
gather together like this.
I came here today to
ask some favors of you.
For the upcoming Chupakabura
Founding Festival,
we are planning on making the
main event a trivia contest,
open to anyone who
wants to participate.
We anticipate it being popular.
However, we don't
have enough staff,
so if anyone here would
be available to volunteer,
we'd certainly
appreciate your help.
Can I be blunt here? If you
don't have enough people,
why don't you just do what
you can with what you have?
Maybe limit the participants?
Thanks for that point,
Takamizawa.
The festival's purpose is to
introduce as many people as
we can to the town.
The trivia questions will even
be set up to teach people
all about Manoyaman
products and landmarks.
The members of the board will
already have their hands full
running the food stalls.
[NOGE] Do you think anyone
will actually show up?
We had that one Founding
Festival ten years ago,
but it was a big flop.
Nobody goes to the
Kingdom itself anymore.
Well, we have news for you!
Ptolemaios will be coming to
play at the Founding Festival!
[TOWNSFOLK]
Huh?
[ANGELICA]
Wait, like the astronomer?
They're a super popular
band right now!
You know, they've got that
song in the soda commercial?
Oh!
[YOSHINO] We're working with
the TV network's event division,
so we'll have more
attendees than ever before!
It's a perfect opportunity to
raise interest in Manoyama!
You mentioned a second favor.
What's that about?
It's about the prize
for the trivia contest.
What we'd like to do is give out
coupons that can be used
all around Manoyama to
anyone who participates.
They'd be 500 yen a person,
and look like this.
But who will cover the cost
of those goods and services?
We can't possibly use
the city's subsidies
for something like that, can we?
Correct, we can't.
And we weren't able to raise as
many sponsorships as we needed.
Oh, no! Why was that?
Go ahead and pull that
back to a wide shot.
[NUNOBE] Are you telling us
that we should sacrifice
for the stupid Kingdom? Why on
earth would we ever do that?
I'm sure that it probably sounds
like a very selfish request,
but we truly need your help
to make the Founding
Festival a success!
Well isn't that
convenient for you?
[YOSHINO gasps]
Convenient?
Don't give up.
This is for the town, isn't it?
This is for your hometown,
am I right?
Don't you want the town
you live in to bustle?
To come alive and keep growing?
Isn't it important to get people
to come back to Manoyama,
over and over?
Again and again?
You don't understand.
Think about it.
Getting more tourists isn't
actually going to help
a bookstore!
Or a tatami mat shop, either.
Okay, then, what if we
limited it to restaurants?
Then you ought to make the bus
free for them at the same time.
Don't be ridiculous.
[NOGE] That's what
they're basically saying,
though, isn't it?
You know. I think
it's a great idea.
[MEN]
Huh?
[KUMANO] These people are making
the trip all the way out here
after all and
that's something.
We can give them
a little discount
and if they tell their
friends, we'll profit!
[ANGELICA]
Hm. Well, Yoshi, I'm in.
Thanks, Angelica.
Each of our products
are pretty expensive,
so I'm not sure how
much it'll help you,
but it feels a whole lot
better than doing nothing.
Don't you think so?
Alright, Yoshino. This festival
is for Manoyama, correct?
Since that's the case,
the Board of Merchants
will lighten your load.
Will you, really?!
But surely you don't expect
all of us to participate!
The Board of Merchants has
always had a reserve fund,
hasn't it?
If we don't use it at time
like this, when would we?
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
Okay, the Community Club is in!
We don't have money,
but we have volunteers!
Uh, me too?
They organized the
matchmaking tour for you!
Well, I guess I could
maybe volunteer.
Everyone. Thank you
so very much!
If we're going to do it, we
might as well do it right,
is what I think.
[TAKAMIZAWA] We're behind you,
Queen! And you, ministers!
[KUMANO sighs]
[ANGELICA sighs]
[YOSHINO giggles]
Thank you again, everyone!
This is great!
Yeah!
[AMAMIYA] Okay, I've got a
question for you, Queen.
Alright!
[AMAMIYA]
Can you tell me, honestly,
what effect your efforts
at rural rejuvenation
have had on the town so far?
Well, I-- nope!
You'll see at the festival!
[hammering]
[USHIMATSU]
It's almost here.
[YOSHINO]
Yeah.
It's weird, I feel like they're
trying to show us how much
more they have invested in this.
Well, what I say is, if we
can use it, we should.
I guess, if it'll make
everyone happy, then yeah.
Just like the song, though,
it started with a mistake.
Huh?
You're doing a really
good job here, kid.
Your hard work brings glory to
the name of the Queen, chupa.
I think you're being
way too kind, kabura.
--[YOSHINO snores]
--[footsteps]
[SANAE]
Wake up, Yoshino!
We've got a big
problem on our hands!
[YOSHINO groans]
Huh?
[ALL pant]
Wha--?
[SANAE] I think they showed up
a little early for the show.
[YOSHINO]
That many of them?
It's gonna be one crazy
adventure tomorrow,
don't you think, Queen?
Yep... Crazy!
♪
[SANDAL] If you build it,
he will come.
But once he gets there,
he'll hang around for a while,
and won't go away.
Next time:
"The Marionette's Banquet."