[MAKI] What? Mr. Kadota
went to Kanazawa?
[YOSHINO]
It's okay.
He apparently swore
that he'd be back in time!
Still, though, will he even
be able to find the guy?
Kanazawa's a pretty
big place, you know.
I'll contact Mayor
Naumann on social media
so he can keep
an eye out for him.
It would probably help if
he wore something distinctive.
[USHIMATSU]
What? Something distinctive?
[YOSHINO]
Right!
You've got to
put something on that
will be super easy to spot!
Easy to spot.
[USHIMATSU]
Naumann?
You? Naumann?
[MAN B]
Mon dieu!
Hello, excuse me, sir.
[OFFICER B]
Would you mind coming with us
for a little chat, please?
[USHIMATSU]
Wait, what are you doing?
Let me go! There's no time!
[SANAE] Not quite the
exposure we were looking for.
Man, it's no wonder
they took him in.
Chupakabura interrogation.
I've already told you,
I was waiting for someone!
How many times do I need
to say that to you people?
[NAUMANN]
Excuse me, I'm lost.
Do you know where
the Chupa-- Huh?
[USHIMATSU]
You, Naumann?
Yeah!
I can't believe I found you!
I found you!
Oh, you found him!
That's so great!
That's right!
The mighty, all-powerful
Chupa works in mysterious ways!
Sure, drive safely
on your way back!
Thank goodness!
Sounds like he'll
be back in time!
Do you guys know where Doku is?
The Hanging Toro lanterns in the
temple district won't turn on!
Doku was in the 5-DX when
I saw him a few minutes ago!
Hey, Mino, come take
over the 5-DX for Doku
[MINO]
What? Me?
[MEN] Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Well, Doku? Whaddya think?
[DOKU]
Oh, it'll be just fine.
All fixed. Try turning it on.
There!
Look at that, it does look good.
[NAGISA]
Guess who, Yoshino!
[DOKU]
Huh?
Nagisa? Mom? Dad?
What's going on?
Oh! Is this the queen's family?
Thanks for helping
look after my daughter.
Not at all,
she didn't need me for that.
You guys have fun, Queen.
[YOSHINO]
Thanks, Doku!
[NAGISA chuckles]
Were you shocked?
[YOSHINO]
I still am, actually!
I wish you all had told
me you were coming!
We thought it might be
more fun to surprise you.
[YAE] I'm so glad to
see you're doing well.
You really are the queen
of this town, aren't you?
That's right.
Around these parts,
I'm known as Her Majesty,
Queen Yoshino!
Have you already been
by to see Sakura Pond?
Yeah!
The cherry blossoms
were beautiful.
I think it was about
this time of year
when we first brought
her here, right, honey?
Oh, it was springtime?
That's so perfect!
[AMAMIYA]
A family reunion.
Honestly, a wonderful scene.
Do you mind if I film you folks?
Amamiya!
[AMAMIYA]
Now don't you to worry.
I'm not giving any
of it to Kume.
I've got some time to fill on
the evening news broadcast.
Honestly, I worked
pretty hard for it!
[MEN] Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Are you nervous at all, Ririko?
Yeah, a little.
When you're nervous,
you should write the character
for "person" on your palm
three times, and swallow them.
You do it like this.
Is that what you used to do,
back when you would sing?
[CHITOSE]
Yes.
That's how I know you're
going to be just fine.
You're my
granddaughter, after all.
Do you think he'll make it?
If Mr. Kadota's not here
soon, we're in trouble.
Has he been in contact?
He said that he's
heading here, now.
Hopefully, he's not
hitting any traffic.
[ringing]
[USHIMATSU]
Welp, we've got a problem!
[NAUMANN]
Oh! What a beautiful view!
Yeah...
What? You ran out of gas?
I'll go pick them up right now!
Okay great, can you go with her?
That way, maybe you can
do his makeup in the car.
I think Sanae's car is
parked out behind the tent.
There are too many roads
blocked off for the festival.
You can't possibly
get the car out
from behind the pond right now!
My car is parked over
at the tourism center!
Why don't you you
guys just take that?
But how do we get
to the tourism center?
We'll have to run over there!
[MEN] Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Excuse us!
How's it looking?
Will we make it?
Yep! No worries!
Huh?
Sanae told me what was up!
Let's go!
[USHIMATSU] Wait-o! You can
trust me. Ushimatsu! Okay?
Right, Ushimatsu.
Huh? Huh?! Is that them?
Hey! Right here! Over here!
Mr. Kadota is on his way here.
Don't worry, he'll make it
in plenty of time for the show.
[KAKIMURA]
All right!
Finally here, huh?
[MAKI]
Mm-hm.
Dad's coming to watch, you know.
Yeah, I know.
Tell him to try and film
the whole stage this time.
Oh, come on.
Let him film what he wants,
at least for today.
How're you, Erika? Nervous?
No, I'm not. Are you really...
[KOSUKE]
Hmm?
Are you really
planning to stay here
and be a taiko drummer?
I don't know what's
going to happen in the future.
I'm not sure if I can make a
living doing only that, y'know.
But... for right now,
I'm pretty set on it.
What about you?
[ERIKA] I don't claim to know
what's going to happen, either,
but I'm pretty set
on something, too.
What's that?
It's a secret.
Looks like he'll
get here pretty soon.
Okay. Yeah, I got it!
It's gonna be okay!
Kindaichi will be able
to lead them through!
A happi. Cool, I'm happy!
Okay.
Takamizawa,
make a right turn up here!
[NAUMANN]
Whoa! This is exciting!
Should we try to go
around the shrine float?
No, you've got
to walk from here!
Take the forest path
until you get to the palace!
I'm the directions guy.
Paths between rice fields,
wild animals' trails.
I know every single
route in Manoyama!
There aren't really any
bears here, are there?
Nah, the sound of the festival
should keep 'em well away.
But if things get rough,
I'll protect you.
Where's Mayor Naumann?
What the?
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Hey, wait, why are you here?
[NAUMANN]
Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
You like to wasshoi?
Yes! I wanna wasshoi!
I have idea! Everyone!
Sorry about this.
Do you mind if we
cut in here, though?
Thank you, thank you!
Wasshoi "rn"?
It's cool!
Sounds like he's
carrying the shrine float!
[SHIORI]
Apparently Mayor Naumann
is wasshoi-ing "right now"!
--Huh?
[DOKU]
There they are!
Well, it looks like you
made it this time, Beef.
[USHIMATSU]
Yes! I kept my promise.
Ha! And it only took
you 50 years to do it.
I brought Mayor
Naumann here with me.
If the sister city
thing goes through,
even if the absorption does
end up happening,
Manoyaman customs
and culture will still live on!
I made up my mind 50 years ago.
I'm not running away!
I'm going to
wake up this little town!
Okay, you guys,
it's finally time!
The shrine float has arrived.
So, let's get out there
and give 'em a great show!
Yeah!
Hey, Grandma.
If everything
goes well with my song.
I have something
important to ask you.
[CHITOSE]
Hmm?
I'm here.
I've finally arrived
at this place.
It's been a difficult journey.
I wonder if I can
get along here,
in this little village
full of humans.
I wonder, if we could
share our knowledge,
and live here
peaceably together.
Huh? Who on earth are you?
I've never seen you before!
What is it,
people of the village?
[SHIBUKAWA]
Oh, it's the Chief!
Amazing.
[MAKI]
I bear you no grudge.
You wanted to know me.
You actually wanted to join
hands and understand me.
And for that, I thank you.
♪ Sleep tonight, go and dream ♪
♪ Feel the comfort of our song ♪
♪ A peace missing, alone ♪
♪ Frightened and seeking home ♪
♪ Please forgive us for all
we should have known ♪
♪ Different though we may be ♪
♪ We still can live
here and be free ♪
♪ We all have hearts
pounding strong ♪
♪ Hear the words of this song ♪
♪ And sleep happily,
knowing you are home ♪
[RIRIKO]
♪ Sleep tonight, go and dream ♪
♪ May your spirit
find its peace ♪
♪ Let's light the
flame of this spark ♪
♪ Drive away all the dark ♪
♪ As we joyously
celebrate our own. ♪
♪ Different though we all are ♪
♪ We're struggling
with our truths thus far ♪
♪ Courageously, we join hands ♪
♪ Overcome, understand ♪
♪ And we welcome you,
with our humble song. ♪
♪ Sleep tonight, sleep tonight ♪
♪ So you can, dream peacefully ♪
[YOSHINO] That was such
great work, everyone! Cheers!
[CROWD]
Cheers!
[TAIRA]
Whoa! I'm on TV!
[SHIBUKAWA]
Man, I got cut off!
Hang on, Maki,
play it one more time!
Sure, I'll put it
on slow-mo for ya.
The festival was a hit!
Your granddaughter got up
there and sang wonderfully,
so how about a song
from you, Olive?
Yeah, you could bring
the Garage Band back.
Oh, yes, I would
love to hear that!
You say that, but the reality
might be too much for you.
I couldn't believe it.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Looks like spring has sprung
for Kindaichi over there.
I've always preferred
summer, myself.
A season of heat
for passionate lovers!
Let's have a matchmaking
tour during the summer!
Summer in Manoyama should be
more than hot enough for you!
Ushimatsu!
Naumann!
My buddy!
I can't believe it, but we might
actually get a sister city!
You think the
sister city will happen?
It's certainly possible.
Cool, I've never
met a nun before.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Hey there, Queen.
This year's really
been loads of fun.
Thanks to all your hard work.
Coming from the former prince,
that's an honor to hear.
We'll make it an even
bigger festival next year.
And I'll be one of the guys
carrying the shrine float!
Do it!
[SANAE]
Phew! I might've drunk too much.
Wait a sec, is
Riichan drunk, too?
You actually drank?
Yeah, my very first time.
It feels kind of good.
[YOSHINO sighs]
How beautiful.
Cherry blossoms and a starry sky
make good collaborators.
[SHIORI]
We had a meeting
under the cherry blossoms,
you remember?
[MAKI]
Yeah, it's been a whole year.
[RIRIKO]
It went by so fast.
[SANAE] We got to have some
silly adventures, though.
[MAKI] It might've been silly,
but it was crazy fun.
I wish we could have some more.
[YOSHINO]
Then you should!
Keep doing it! There's a saying.
"Show silliness,
recklessness, and filial piety
while you still can!"
[RIRIKO]
Who said that?
The Second Queen of
the Kingdom of Chupakabura!
That's you, you dork!
[laughter]
[SHIORI] Still, I guess this
is the end of this team, huh?
[YOSHINO] We've got the
abdication ceremony though.
[RIRIKO]
This is just the beginning.
[SANAE]
That's right.
Even if we're no longer
the queen and her ministers,
we still have our
whole future ahead of us.
[MAKI]
What'll you do, Sanae?
I'm going to open a
regional consulting office
in the shopping district.
Akiyama said he'd
let me rent his store,
so I'm all set, now.
What about you?
Have you thought about
what your next play is gonna be?
Uh-huh. This went so well
I want to do something based
on another Manoyaman folk tale.
There are a lot of them.
I could help you.
Oh, Riichan,
you could totally be
the acting troupe's
new playwright!
Have you found something else
you want to do instead?
[RIRIKO]
Mm-hmm.
I made a promise
with my grandma.
I said if I successfully
sang on stage,
I wanted to leave Manoyama.
[gasps]
You're really leaving town?
I wanna see the world,
with my own eyes.
But don't worry, I'll be back.
You have to send
lots of pictures.
I will.
Actually, I've
made up my mind, too.
What I'm gonna do
right now, and the future.
You've decided
to leave us, then.
[YOSHINO]
Yeah.
I think Manoyama is
a really lovely place.
I've learned so much
from all of you guys
over the past year,
And I've felt at home here.
But, I... I don't feel
like it's time for me
to surrender to that
feeling, you know?
I think it's great.
You're making an
honest choice for yourself.
I can get behind that.
Yeah, so can we. Right?
Thanks so much, you guys.
Manoyama really is a
second hometown to me!
Well, I promise,
I'm going to do my
very best to look after it,
so it'll be all ready for you
whenever you want to come back!
Hey, let's all raise our
glasses, one more time!
[MAKI]
To bright futures for everyone!
[ALL]
Cheers!
Mr. Kadota.
[USHIMATSU]
Hey, you're up early, Queen.
[YOSHINO]
Yeah. Good morning.
[USHIMATSU] The last year
went by in a flash, huh?
[YOSHINO]
It did.
[USHIMATSU] I guess you've
made up your mind, then.
[YOSHINO]
I'm sorry.
[USHIMATSU]
No, no need to apologize.
It was a one-year contract.
It's better for you
to leave, anyhow.
If you stick around
here long enough,
then you won't be
an outsider anymore,
and that's no fun, right?
What are you planning to
do about the next queen?
Well, I've thought about it,
and I've finally come
to a decision on that.
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
Hey, come on,
it's about to start!
When I first came here
to the town of Manoyama,
I was totally unaware
of what it was.
I honestly assumed it was
just another country town
out in the sticks.
A "normal" little place
without much going for it.
But over the past year,
I've lived and worked
in Manoyama,
and I've met so many
different kinds of people here.
And before I knew it,
I realized that while
it might seem "normal,"
there are so many
things about Manoyama
that are completely unique.
Its own special history.
Its own special culture.
Its own special scenery.
These are things that Manoyama
has cultivated over a
long, long period of time.
Things that are truly precious,
that you'll never
find anywhere else.
Manoyama cherishes its
history and its culture,
and at the same time,
it's open and continues
to grow and change.
So, even if it was
only for a short time,
it has truly been this
foolish outsider's honor
to serve you.
Today marks the end of
my term as your queen,
so I'll say goodbye.
Thank you so much, everyone!
Thank you for making this
the best year of my life!
There is something that
Manoyama has cherished
for a very long time now:.
The ideal that was
clearly expressed
in the dragon song:
Do not reject other cultures.
Make their knowledge
a part of you.
Share and change with
the world, and you'll live on.
Some of us here had almost
forgotten about that ideal,
but this queen--this young,
foolish, outsider,
was able to
remind us who we are.
That's why I've made up my mind.
We don't need the Kingdom
of Chupakabura anymore!
Every individual person
in Manoyama can think
and learn, pass
down their culture,
and occasionally,
change and grow.
And we'll always be
proud of who we are,
and of Manoyama.
Effective immediately,
I hereby relieve the
queen of her duties,
and disband the
Kingdom of Chupakabura!
It truly was a wonderful year.
One for the books.
And for that,
Queen, I thank you.
Okay, Manoyama,
I think we should give it up
for the queen,
one more time, huh?
[SANAE]
Yoshino! Are you coming?
Yeah! On my way!
[MAKI]
Okay, that should do it.
[YOSHINO] This tree is
here for the five of us.
[SANAE] You think maybe
we should bury a time capsule
while we're at it?
You know what?
I want to keep planting
lots and lots
of cherry trees around here,
and Manoyama will
be known as a city
full of cherry blossoms!
I love that!
And so, then, no matter
if we're talking about ten years
down the road or a hundred,
Manoyama will always have them!
I hope that we'll
all be able to see
those blossoms
here together someday.
[YAMADA]
We're gonna miss you.
But don't worry,
the town's in good hands.
[MINO]
The Manoyama Tourism Board team
will always be in
our hearts, right?
Right!
Where is he?
Sorry, he said
he couldn't make it.
Oh. All right!
Thanks guys, time to go.
Take care, girl!
We'll schedule
a show in your area.
Good luck over there, Yoshi.
Come back for next year's
Mizuchi Festival, okay?
[YOSHINO]
Mm.
I wouldn't miss it!
[SHIORI, MAKI]
Yoshino!
[MINO]
We love you, Queen! Be safe!
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
No way!
Bye, Kindaichi!
Doku! Bye, Chitose!
[laughs]
Huh?
Yoshino Koharu!
This is your town, forever!
You'll always have a home here!
You wrote my name wrong again!
[SANDAL]
And so, the queen departs,
having made the town
a little happier,
and becoming quite
happy herself in the process.
[SANDAL]
But, the townspeople's adventure
is only just beginning.
And the queen is beginning
a new adventure of her own.
Though, not where
she thought she would.
[SANDAL] You see, the queen
didn't decide to return
to Tokyo or go back
to the countryside.
She took another path.
[exhales]
Man, that was a close one.
Yoshino Koharu!
From the Momonga
Promotion Agency!
So nice to meet you!
[SANDAL]
All's well that ends well.
Thank you for
watching Sakura Quest.