[music playing]
Feels like I lost a bet.
Why? It's a parade to introduce
you as the new queen!
At this rate, you should
just put me in the stocks!
Oh, don't be silly, Yoshi.
What's the point of
putting you in the stocks
if there's nobody to see it?
[music continues]
Turn it down!
You gonna make me?
Don't you know "It Always
Starts with a Mistake"
by Yoshino Tsubaki
when you hear it,
you classless idiot?
[music continues]
Kinda long day huh?
That's a bit of
an understatement.
Oh, no thanks!
We just came in to eat today.
Hey, it's Maki.
On a date?
Do you think that's
a boyfriend from Tokyo?
Nope, he's my brother, Kosuke.
Thanks for looking after my sis.
Anyway, I don't think
there's much else to say.
Tell Mom for me, would you?
I won't be coming
home any time soon.
[KOSUKE sighs]
Okay, whatever you say.
So, are you the new queen?
The one they brought
in from Tokyo?
Um, yeah, I am.
Well, good luck with that.
I hope that you can bring
a little life to this place.
It's great to meet you.
Oh, yeah, thank you.
Same to you.
[SHIORI] So you're pretty
resolved not to move back home,
huh, Maki?
[MAKI]
Yeah, not for a while, anyway.
I think I get that.
Hard to believe
it was so lively in here
a few days ago.
Well, Sanae's got her own work,
so I guess that's
just the way it goes.
Hey, if you're a little
lonely here on your own,
I could always move in with you.
Seriously?
It's here!
What? Not more manju.
[YOSHINO] No.
It's all my stuff from Tokyo.
I kept bugging my manager
until he finally sent it.
So I guess you've
made up your mind, then.
I'll go ahead and
give it a shot,
for now, anyway.
At least it's not boring.
And there are worse
things than being paid
to be a queen, wouldn't you say?
I kinda doubt it'll be
quite as easy as you think.
Today's public service
will be an interview--
a local station.
Your first proper interview!
[chuckles]
You've got a script
and a cheat sheet.
No worries, right?
There's nothing
to be nervous about!
Time to get going, Queen.
[KUME]
Oh, I see.
So, the Head of
the Tourism Board
mistook you for the
old star, Yoshino Tsubaki,
and that's what brought
you to Manoyama.
Right!
But even starting as a mistake,
I'm going to stay and
give it my very best shot!
I've heard a rumor
that you're also entering
the Regional Mascot Contest
that's happening next week!
Yep! And we hope that people
will turn out to support us!
[USHIMATSU growls]
Must've been a shock
learning about this whole
Kingdom of Chupakabura thing!
Yes! I honestly had no clue
what it was about at first,
but after looking into it a bit,
I found it really interesting.
It's basically one of the old
mini independent states,
but they've built a story
for it and everything,
and it's fantastic!
Oh.
[YOSHINO]
Umm...
You see, it all started in
the 457th year of the Chupa--
[KUME] Right, right,
I think we're all familiar
with the backstory.
Now, there've been great
efforts to reinvigorate
small towns all across Japan.
Surely you are aware
that very few of them
have succeeded.
That's the big issue
you've committed to tackle
for the next year.
Uh-huh.
[KUME] As queen, what are
your thoughts on any changes
you'd like to make to the town?
That question's
not in the script!
Come on, hang in there, Queen!
All right, on to
the next quesion, then!
What are some of your favorite
things about Manoyama?
Umm... I would say
the beautiful scenery?
And stuff?
[KUME]
There are several products made
right here in town.
Do you have a
particular favorite?
Umm, I guess maybe the manju?
[KUME] So what made you
decide to continue as queen?
If it was a mistake,
you could have refused, right?
[YOSHINO] Well, yes, but I was
impressed by this company's--
er, this town's potential for
growth and its company culture?
[SHIORI]
No, no worries at all, Yoshi!
Honestly, I think I started
to believe my own press,
being called "Queen"
and everything.
But I don't know
a thing about this town.
Well, you know what?
It's never too late
to start learning!
That's right!
And we can all help teach you.
Look at all the resources
we have here!
Idiots!
[YAMADA, MINO gasp]
[USHIMATSU]
She won't learn about the town
by reading a bunch of studies!
She's gotta be in it!
Feel the wind! On her face!
What do you think, Yoshi?
Feeling anything?
What I'm feeling...
[sighs] ...is nothing at all.
I'm so sorry!
It's okay.
Hey, why don't you talk
to that lady over there?
Excuse me! Hi, there!
I'm the new queen.
Do you have a minute?
I'd love to chat with
you about... uh...
Pardon me!
Can you tell me a
little about the town?
What's the best
thing about Manoyama?
[OLD WOMAN 3A]
What? Who's wrestling?
[YOSHINO]
No, not wrestling!
What's the best thing
about Manoyama?
I'll tell you, it's certainly
not the wrestling.
If you had a chance
to change Manoyama,
what kind of town
would you like it to be?
Things are fine as they are.
I don't see a reason
to change anything
when it's working just fine.
What about the
future of the town?
[YOSHINO]
Well, for instance,
what about improvements?
Like, are there any changes
you might want to make
if you could?
[SHOP OWNER 3B] Why? Talking
to you won't change anything.
What good could
an outsider possibly do?
C'mon, no worries!
I think you just
happened to talk to
some of the wrong people.
There are plenty
of folks around here
who care an awful lot
about the town!
Everything good?
Oh hey, it's the queen!
[SHIORI]
What's going on, officer?
Aw, just got a
few reports saying
some strange-looking girl
has been wandering around
blathering some
nonsense about how
she was going to "go home."
Well, ouch, that hurts.
To be fair, though,
a lot of people
haven't met you yet.
I mean, I know Ushimatsu
has been working
really hard on this,
but to tell the absolute truth,
most people couldn't
care less about
bringing change to this town.
And why do you think
that is, exactly?
[NOGE] The thing is,
we've been getting along okay.
The town's been surviving
for a while now
with hardly any tourists at all.
Although, the future's
not bright or anything.
It's not like many kids
are born here.
But I doubt I'll still
be running this store
when it gets to be a problem.
So, no point fighting it,
you know?
Seriously?
[NOGE] Yeah, that's basically
how I feel about it.
I'd be surprised if most
didn't feel the same.
You might also
check in with the head
of the Board of
Merchants, though.
Board of Merchants?
Rii- chan 's grandma is
actually the head of that board.
but she doesn't get along
with Mr. Kadota, remember?
Well I'm going over there.
Yoshi, wait!
What do you want, Queen?
I don't have all day.
We just came by to say hello.
Come back yesterday.
[YOSHINO gasps]
We can't come back yesterday!
Please, can't we talk to you?
[SHIORI] Come on, Yoshi, we'll
try another time, Thank you!
Hey! Working hard today,
huh, Queen?
[YOSHINO] Mr. Takamizawa,
isn't that right?
You're the bus driver
I met before.
Yep, that's me.
I might not look it anymore, but
I used to be a prince, you know.
What do you mean, a prince?
Oh, my gosh!
What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Suddenly, I feel about a
bazillion years old, that's all.
[ERIKA] It's not gonna
matter what you do, Queen.
This is a crappy old
town way beyond saving.
Give it up.
Hey.
Apologize, Erika.
[ERIKA]
No!
I called it crappy
because it's crappy!
[TAKAMIZAWA sighs]
Welp, don't let
her discourage you.
You know the old saying, right?
Changemakers are the youth,
fools, and outsiders.
The funny thing is, Ushimatsu
used to be a young fool
long ago, but he definitely
wasn't ever an outsider.
[MAKI] Seems you're pretty
much the ideal candidate.
Just a youthful,
foolish outsider.
[YOSHINO]
Sanae is, too, then!
That doesn't work
because I'm not a fool.
I guess you must've
missed us pretty bad.
Couldn't stay away?
[SANAE] I'm just taking refuge
while the exterminators
clear my house.
Isn't it weird?
How it used to be
the Kingdom of Kabura?
Yeah, it is weird!
I just heard about that today.
[TAKAMIZAWA] The reason was
that kabura are Manoyama's
only real specialty.
Kabura ? We call them kabu .
[SHIORI] Yeah, around here,
people call them kabura .
It was back before I had even
started elementary school.
They used rural
stimulation funds to create
the Kingdom of kabura .
But it didn't last very long.
That was when Ushimatsu had
that big idea of his own.
"The ones that can
change our city are the youth,
outsiders, fools, and of
course, the monsters!"
And so, they decided
to hop on the UMA bandwagon,
changing the kingdom's name from
kabura to Chupakabura.
That's nuts!
The Board of Merchants
was completely against the idea
from the very beginning.
Well, I would be, too,
because I'm not nuts.
I've got it!
Got what?
It's kabura !
Everyone in Manoyama really
loves the stuff, right?
So kabura must be the secret
to changing the town!
[WOMAN 3A]
You want to observe the farming?
We harvest the kabura in winter.
So I'm afraid there's
not much to do now.
Well, maybe you
could just tell me why
you're so passionate
about kabura .
Oh, I wouldn't say
that I'm passionate.
We've just been growing
them around here
for a long time, that's all.
But look, you've got
a Kabura Kid over there!
[WOMAN 3A]
Oh.
Yeah, sure, our son
used to like him a lot.
Oh! He's probably farming
kabura now, too, then, right?
No, he left town
and got a job.
Doesn't come back
here much anymore.
[SHIORI humming]
Oh, good morning.
Good morning.
Hey, where's the queen?
They're holding the Regional
Mascot Contest in town,
so she's headed that
way with Mr. Kadota.
And I'll be going over
to help them this afternoon!
Man, aren't you the busy bee.
Oh, the broadcast
should be starting now!
[MAKI] We're putting the
Chupakabura up against those?
The kids are gonna cry.
[phone ringing]
--Hi, there!
--[MINO] Shiori, listen!
Have you seen the
Chupakabura's head?
[SHIORI]
Huh?
It's not in here, sorry.
No, I told you, we can't
find the thing anywhere!
You're saying it's
not there, either?
Unfortunately not.
We're asking Shiori
about it right now.
Yeah, she doesn't know.
Well, you better figure it out!
We go on at three and I
want that Chupakabura head
here by then!
[YAMADA]
But we--
How is the head
the only thing missing?
[MINO]
What?!
Why would you throw it away?!
How's this?
[YOSHINO] Well, if we
wanna scare kids, it's great.
[KIDS]
Uhh...
[KIDS scream]
You're not helping--stop it!
[TV 3A] Mascots from near
and far are eagerly awaiting--
He is such a stupid ass.
[TV 3A] The air is
full of excitement!
[CHITOSE chuckles]
[CHITOSE] Ririko,
come down here, would you?
[SANAE]
Hello, all!
And how is the queen today?
[MAKI]
You've got a lot of free time.
Hey, shut it, Oden!
[MAKI]
Don't call me that.
Could I get both of
you to focus, please?
We should be thinking
of a way to get Yoshi
and Mr. Kadota out of this mess!
[door opens]
[SHIORI]
Rii- chan !
Kabura Kid.
[RIRIKO]
I saw on TV.
If you use the
Kabura Kid costume
instead of the Chupakabura,
that would solve your problem.
Oh, my gosh, that's right!
There's a costume
from when we were
the Kingdom of Kabura!
That old man destroyed
the Kingdom of Kabura
by himself, and now
he's going to be saved
by the Kabura Kid.
How perfectly humiliating.
That's good TV.
[RIRIKO]
But then, the mascot entry
wouldn't be the Chupakabura.
We can't really
afford to be concerned
about that right now.
Do you know where
the costume is?
It's no use.
I can't find it anywhere.
You think maybe
it got thrown away?
Or it could be someone
took it somewhere
to use it and
never returned it.
[SHIORI]
Oh, I hope not.
[SANAE]
We're not giving up yet!
Around when did they switch from
the Kingdom of Kabura
to Chupakabura?
If I remember correctly,
I think it was August of 1997.
August '97--looks like
that's spot-on.
This might be
Kabura Kid's last event.
[SHIORI] Wow!
I didn't know this existed!
[SANAE] Wow, look at that
nineties home video quality.
[MAKI] That might be the
Manoyama Community Center.
Hey, that looks like
the Tanaka Fabric store.
That place is still around!
Spoken like a true detective.
So it's possible that it was
used at the Community Center,
and then never returned
to the palace.
This guy's just as energetic
as he can be, isn't he?
It's Doggon!
[YOSHINO]
Oh, man.
Am I gonna have
to go out there alone?
I have to say, I can't help
but think they might've tried
a little too hard
and missed the mark.
Oh. Found it.
[SANAE]
I know I'm stating the obvious,
but that's pretty beaten up.
[MAKI] I think I should be able
to fix it up enough to pass.
[fabric ripping]
How do you have such
a wide range of skills?
Because I used to make
props as a side job.
I want this one.
Can you see okay?
[CROWD chattering]
[KUME] All right!
Let's welcome the next mascot!
[CROWD clapping]
Oh, boy.
Looks like I'll have
to go up by myself.
You wouldn't survive.
That's too much
pressure for a person
who failed 30 job interviews.
[engine running]
We're here!
Oh, hey, you guys.
What's that?
It's Kabura Kid,
and Mr. Kadota should use it!
Where did you find that?!
Mr. Kadota! We've got it!
It was in the garbage
processing plant!
Gross!
Sorry, sir, but you
gotta put it on!
No, it stinks!
[SHIORI]
Then use this instead!
No way!
I refuse to be the Kabura Kid!
[MINO] Then you've got
to be the Chupakabura!
[USHIMATSU] I can't wear that!
It smells terrible!
[YAMADA]
So breathe through your mouth!
I said no and I meant it!
[overlapping chatter]
At least wash it!
Doesn't matter
which one you wear!
[GROUP]
Huh?
Are you kidding me?
Idiot! Of course it matters!
I'm doing everything I can
to change this town!
I know you are,
but the problem is
nobody in Manoyama
actually wants it to change
--but you!
--What do you know?
You just got here,
and you're a kid!
One thing I know is that
you've stubbornly stuck
to the Chupakabura
thing for decades,
and so far,
nothing's changed, right?
The Chupakabura is up next,
so please be ready
when I call you!
Fine, then.
If the queen's so sure about it,
then why doesn't she
decide which one to use?
[CROWD clapping]
Okay, for our next contestant,
we've got the Chupakabura
from Manoyama!
Well, would you look at that.
This one sure looks different
from his application photo.
Yes. He's changed a little.
That's pretty smart of her.
She neither rejected nor
chose either one of them.
It's like a mashup of the two.
Necessity's the
mother of invention.
I hope she'll be able
to speak well this time.
[USHIMATSU growling]
Years ago, in Manoyama,
the Kabura Kid was chosen
as the town's mascot.
Kabura was an obvious choice,
because Manoyama has a history
of growing quality kabura .
But unfortunately,
Kabura Kid was never very
beloved by the town folk.
Something had to be done,
and UMAs were very popular,
so they made their next
mascot the Chupakabura.
And when they did,
they really hoped
that people would
take to it this time.
But he wasn't
very popular either.
Kabura Kid and Chupakabura--
Neither of them ever managed
to become very dear
to the good people of Manoyama.
Over time, both of
them were forgotten.
That's why it doesn't
matter which one he is.
That's not what's important.
Sometimes we focus
on the wrong things.
So, the question is,
just what is important
to the community
of Manoyama?
What is it that drives them?
What stands the test of time?
What means most to them?
What about the town is unique?
What do they hold dear?
I'll freely admit this to you.
I've only just gotten
here myself,
so I don't know the
answer to this yet.
You seriously don't know?
[YOSHINO] However, I want
to discover the answer.
And I'll spend
the next year trying.
With the gracious help of all
my new friends here, of course.
I feel like that's my job,
and I'll do my best
to be a great queen!
[CROWD clapping]
[GROUP]
Cheers!
I couldn't have done it
without you guys!
Thanks so much!
[SANAE]
Don't worry about it!
I feel sure we'll be able
to come up with a way
for you to repay us.
Come on, we did
come in third to last,
after all.
True, maybe if you'd
pepped up that speech
and told a few jokes.
[MAKI] I can see why you failed
all 30 of those interviews.
Hey, she was sincere
and spoke from the heart!
I thought it was
really wonderful.
[SANAE] Oh, don't pay
attention to us, Shiori.
We're just teasing her.
Wow, rude.
[GIRLS laugh]
So do you not
drink, Rii- chan ,
or just not tonight?
I'm not a fan of alcohol.
[SANAE]
Why the heck not?
It's so tasty!
[MAKI] You really just want
to get drunk, don't you?
[USHIMATSU] I take it you've
decided to commit to being Queen
for the next year,
after all, eh?
Yes.
But there's something
I've been thinking about.
I have one condition!
Hm? What's that?
I want to work
with these four.
What do you think?
If you guys are with me,
I feel like I have a real shot
at doing some good.
I mean, I really need your help.
Dear Shiori, and Sanae,
and Maki, and Ririko,
would you be willing
to work alongside me,
your new queen?
So, what, is this
a royal command?
It depends on the salary.
You'll do it,
won't you, Rii- chan ?
[RIRIKO]
Mm-hmm.
So?
All right.
Guess we have the
budget for it, Queen.
Sir, you won't regret it!
Sanae can be
the Minister of IT!
And Rii- chan 's
the uma Minister!
[RIRIKO]
It's U.M.A, not "uma."
Will you be Chief Handywoman?
[MAKI]
The hell is that?
How 'bout Minister of Oden?
I'm gonna kill you.
[YOSHINO laughing]
[SANAE]
What? It's perfect!
What's up, Minister of Oden?
[MAKI] Seriously, I'm over
hearing about Oden!
[SANDAL] The ministers
have finally been chosen.
So the queen won't
be lonely anymore.
Next time: "The Lone Alchemist."