[SANAE] Today marks the
beginning of a new journey!
I got a sudden request from
the local tourism board.
I'll be working with
them on a rural rejuvenation
project as the Minister of IT!
So that means I'm moving
out of the old house
where I've been living alone
for the last six months,
and into to a big cabin
with my new friends!
[RIRIKO] Unfortunately,
I'm afraid that means
I'll also be forced
to say goodbye to all
of my little bug pals.
Not cool!
No peeking at my blog!
[MAKI]
Bug pals, huh?
What, are you
writing fiction now?
Shut it, Oden Detective!
Yeah, I have a slightly
different persona in my blog.
That doesn't mean
I'm lying or anything.
[SANAE screams]
Get it, Shiori! Get it!
--[SHIORI] Where is it?
--[SANAE] I don't know! Find it!
[SHIORI]
Umm...
[YOSHINO]
Hey, what's that?
It's amazing!
Ranma .
You've never heard of it?
No, I know about ranma .
I've just never seen
any like this one.
The detail in the carving
is really incredible,
don't you think?
Ranma carving is officially
one of Manoyama's
traditional arts.
There's a wood carving
district in Monzenmachi,
where the shops are,
and there are lots
of sculptors down there!
Wow, I didn't know that.
I don't get how you
could possibly miss it.
What've you been doing here
for the past half year?
Well, what do you think?
I was working, of course!
And I like working
at home a lot,
surrounded by all
of these antiques!
It's very inspiring!
Kind of like combining
the old and the new!
[USHIMATSU sighs]
Finished.
Is the old man here?
What do you want, woman?
Don't pull my granddaughter
into your weird schemes.
What's this "minister" crap?
Ririko joined of
her own free will!
Well, I'm her legal guardian
and I don't like it!
[USHIMATSU] Don't come after me
just 'cause your granddaughter
betrayed you, hag!
[CHITOSE] You'd better
watch what you say to me,
you old ass!
[engine revving]
[SHIORI]
Oh, no, come on.
I wonder if my dad
messed something up
when he tuned it up himself.
Will it be okay?
No, I think it's dead.
Let's ask Doku for help.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess it is time
to bring it to Doku.
Hang on, Doku?
Like, that Doku?
Who's this Doku person?
[doorbell ringing]
[beeping]
[YOSHINO]
A vending machine?
No way!
You gotta be kiddin' me!
It wouldn't transform
for me no matter what I did!
It was you!
How did you do it?
How did you get it to start up?
I-I don't know!
I mean, it wasn't
anything special.
I just kind of touched it!
There it is, then!
That's the answer!
My dried-up hands
don't have the necessary
hyaluronic acid and yours do!
'Kay, that should do it.
Go ahead and try
to start her up.
[YOSHINO]
Oh!
[engine revs, starts]
So he's not just
some weirdo, then.
[MAKI]
Thanks a lot, Doku.
You can send the bill
to the tourism board.
Just make sure
you address it to me.
Ushimatsu sure hasn't
changed, has he?
I kept telling him, it should be
the Kingdom of Mechakabura,
not the Kingdom of Chupakabura.
Not much of an improvement.
Hey, that's right!
You guys are in the middle
of moving, aren't you?
What a perfect opportunity.
[YOSHINO]
What is that?
[DOKUSHIMA] Prototype for
my powered exoskeleton.
The Hercules 2.0!
[chuckles]
Give it a try.
Let me know what you think!
[YOSHINO laughs]
Wow! This thing
is so incredible!
Hey, be careful!
There's a hard drive in there!
Would you like to
try out the suit, too?
Yeah, kinda.
Okay!
Once you're finished with that,
then we can switch!
Hey, hold on a second.
That's not her room;
I thought it was yours!
Oh, I decided to
let Sanae have it.
I'm gonna move into
the loft on the 2nd floor.
You know, I'm not loving
how you make it sound
like I'm totally
in your debt now.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
Guess I'm just happy to
have friends here with me.
It's gonna be so much fun!
Well, don't forget,
my work as Minister
is only a side job.
I've still got my
normal work, too,
so we'll see how
helpful I'll actually be.
I'm starving.
Anyone up for a break?
Move-in noodles.
How 'bout we go to Angelica's?
The special of the day
is katsu curry.
I could cook for us.
I brought some soba noodles
with me from home.
Just give me a few
minutes to boil them!
Look at you!
We've got a domestic
goddess on our hands.
[USHIMATSU]
Listen up, everyone.
Now, I know I've been coming up
with the trials for you.
However, from now on,
you'll have to create
and complete them
all on your own.
So basically,
you ran out of ideas?
Okay.
To make it clear,
Miss Smarty-pants,
the point is, you can't
just hang out here
all day doing nothing!
You need to
think for yourselves!
How can we draw
a bunch of tourists
and make the town some money?
[YOSHINO]
I know!
How 'bout the wood
carving district?
What about it?
Oh, well, I was really
impressed with the ranma
in Sanae's house!
I thought maybe we
could use some of that
to promote the town!
Huh...
I can't wait to start tomorrow!
Okay, what do you
want us to do first?
[YOSHINO]
I think we should check out
the wood carving district.
[SANAE yells]
It's a bean.
Will you chill out?
See? No bug, no worries!
Why did you move
all the way out here
to the country if you
hate bugs so much?
Look, how was I
to know I hated them?
I had to move out here
in order to find that out.
I mean, it's not like
there are tons of bugs
creeping around in Tokyo.
[CHITOSE]
Ririko.
Look, I think it's fine
if you want to work
with the queen.
However, you need to tell me
what you're doing over there.
This is the wood
carving district.
[SANAE] Kinda small
to be called a "district."
[SHIORI] Lots of bushi gathered
here because of all the temples,
so it ended up becoming
a center for wood-carving.
What're bushi ?
Sculptors that carve
Buddhist images.
[SANAE]
Oh.
[YAMADA] The Queen and her
ministers seem pretty excited.
Didn't you tell them that we
tried promoting Manoyama's
wood carving several
times before,
and it failed miserably?
It did not fail.
We just haven't seen
any of the results yet.
With all due respect,
I actually think we have.
He was made honorary mayor
of the wood carving district.
He had a bunch of
Chupakabura figurines carved
and now he's stuck
with a stockpile of 'em.
That sucks.
Listen! Our young queen
from out of town
found it interesting
and I think that says a lot!
She shows more promise
than the two of you idiots!
[MAKI yawns]
Hey, look at these, Sanae!
Aren't they so cute?
But a kabura carving
is a little mundane,
don't you think?
Nah! I think their familiarity
is what makes 'em cute.
[TATSUO]
They make wonderful souvenirs!
We have a special
promotion going on now!
Buy one and you'll get
a Chupakabura figurine,
free of charge!
Oh, wow!
Thanks a lot, but that's
really not necessary.
Also, we can personalize it
by carving your name
into the back!
Hey there, Tatsuo!
Yeah, I'm afraid
they're not tourists!
We're here to check things out
for a wood carving
district PR campaign!
I'm the queen, Yoshino Koharu!
This is Ms. Kouzuki,
Minister of IT.
Oh! The queen and a minister!
I'm so sorry, I had no idea!
I hope you can forgive me.
[chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
[TATSUO]
Oh, you're back early!
Hey, this is the new queen!
Nice to meet you!
This is Kazushi,
the senior apprentice here.
So you both moved to Manoyama
specifically to do this?
Right. Kazushi moved all
the way from Hokkaido.
But I'm just from Osaka.
I moved here from Tokyo!
Oh, that's cool!
Enjoy yourselves.
[TATSUO chuckles]
Sorry, he's not
a very sociable guy.
But he is one of the best
when it comes to sculpting!
And if you're gonna be
promoting Manoyama Wood Carving,
then believe you me, ladies,
we're gonna help out
as much as we can!
[YOSHINO]
That'd be terrific!
Let's get to it!
We need to find a
strategy to draw tourists
to the wood carving district!
And I think we should call it
the WCD Tourism Plan for short!
Oh, one thing first, Yoshi.
I gathered some studies
on our past PR failures.
We don't want to make
the same mistakes,
so I thought we
should review them.
This is going to be difficult
no matter what angle we try.
How much demand could there be
for wood carvings
in the first place?
[SHIORI]
You're right.
These days, few houses
are made with places
to put up sculptures,
and even fewer have ranma .
When I was little,
we had a carving of a bear
on top of our television.
[MAKI]
Now, TVs are so thin,
you can't put anything
on top of 'em.
Hey! Then why don't we
make skinny bears
to match the TVs?
No? Okay, maybe not!
Sculptures might
really be hard to market
because, since they're
carved one at a time,
they're kind of expensive.
Yeah, that's true.
The ones we were looking
at were not cheap.
And can't be mass produced.
It's rough to make a living
from wood-carving alone, too.
So finding people
to carry on the tradition
can be a big problem.
But there are younger
people like the students
we just met, right?
So they are around.
Yes, but apparently, it's a
pretty hard path to follow.
A lot of people will
start out as pupils
and quit before
they've finished.
[YOSHINO]
Hey, come on, you guys!
We've barely even
started this meeting,
and there hasn't been a
single positive comment!
You're right.
Even if the current
market is a bit weak,
I'm sure we can find
a way to revive it!
Wow, somebody's gung-ho.
You in love with
that older sculptor guy?
That's not what this is!
But we're similar because
we both moved to Manoyama
and we're working hard
to make things happen here.
So I want to support them.
You know the old saying.
"We learn from the past."
But it's also time for some
innovation around here!
[TATSUO] There's apparently
a new plan in place
to rejuvenate the town using
Manoyama Wood Carving.
The queen has been
really excited about it!
We're hoping that our woodwork
will become popular
all over the country--
Don't let yourself get caught up
in the tourism
board's foolishness.
You should try to remember,
our wood carving has been named
a traditional art form.
So show some pride.
[YOSHINO sighs]
My brain is completely fried.
Yeah, same.
[SHIORI] Brainstorming sure
takes a lot of energy, huh?
I think our idea about
the wooden katanas
is the most realistic.
[YOSHINO]
I also like the Chupakabura
with a kabura in its mouth.
Especially the fact
that it's thin.
Are you still on that?
Ooh, a new drink!
[SANAE]
Wait, doesn't that have--
A little alcohol
might just get those
creative juices flowing,
you know?
[RIRIKO]
Mokele-mbembe.
[SANAE] I told you,
nobody knows what that is!
[YOSHINO]
Doku!
Oh, the queen!
Tell me, what'd you think
of the Hercules 2.0?
Great! It was actually
super helpful!
I loved being able
to lift such heavy stuff!
Well, personally,
I'd like to see it used
for some kind of
agricultural work,
but the older people
have a hard time accepting
change and progress.
Makes sense.
Also, it felt kind of
stiff or something.
Could be harder for
an older person to use it.
Hmm...
Oh, that's it!
[TATSUO] Carvings on
a powered exoskeleton?
That's right!
Just like this, see?
Well, the sketch leaves
something to be desired, but--
Hey, now!
Basically, it's the same as
putting a case on a smartphone.
Wrapping it up inside
a pretty package.
A true collaboration
between modern,
cutting-edge technology
and traditional art!
Cool, huh?
[clattering]
[TATSUO]
Ah...
Um, let's--let's take our
conversation outside.
Sorry about that.
Kazushi really can't
stand this kind of thing.
Uh... But I think
it's fascinating!
No way, do you really?
Yeah!
I'd love to help out
in any way I can!
Thank you so much for that!
Planting rice using
an exoskeleton
with wood carvings attached
is pretty darn unique, huh?
All we need is a
little news coverage,
then we'll get a
bunch of tourists,
and they'll all buy sculptures
as souvenirs! Voilà!
But what about Kazushi?
Won't he be upset
at you for forging ahead
without his input?
The thing is, that guy
always follows his own path.
If his work is interfered with,
then yeah,
he'll probably get angry.
But I don't think he'll
have much of anything
to say about what we're doing.
I know he may seem
a little eccentric to you,
but seriously, Kazushi's
carvings are just incredible.
They're on par with
the work you see here.
I can't even begin to compete.
So I'll follow my own path, too.
I'll use our ancient art form
to unite the old with the new.
[SHIORI'S DAD chuckles]
It's like I'm wearing
the special effects
on a hero show!
Yes, honey, you're very cool.
You never told me that
your family ran a farm!
It's more of a hobby, really.
Battle mode has been activated.
That should do it.
Try moving around a little.
[SHIORI'S DAD chuckles]
[SHIORI]
You got it, Dad!
Wow! It's so light! Look!
[laughing]
Gosh darn it!
[gasping]
[SHIORI]
Oh, no, catch it!
[TATSUO]
With what?
[SHIORI]
Here, use this!
It did look cool for a minute.
It just wasn't very
practical, that's all.
Shiori, I'm sorry.
Oh, no worries!
My dad really loved it!
He said he had a great time!
I do truly believe we
were on the right track,
though, you know?
Melding tradition with more
modern-day technology.
Oh, that's it, right there!
What's "it"?
We can combine
that transforming
vending machine
at Doku's workshop
with wooden carvings
of a Buddha!
Oh, yeah!
That sounds like a blast, man!
I was just working
on a new drink
for the vending machine
so maybe you
can be my guinea pigs.
This here is Kabura Sushi Soda!
With two percent
kabura sushi extract!
Couldn't you just put
something normal in it?
[DOKUSHIMA]
All right, bring her down slow.
[TATSUO]
Okay!
[DOKUSHIMA, TATSUO grunt]
[YOSHINO]
It's perfect!
[DOKUSHIMA]
There it is.
Hey, why don't you
go give it a test run?
[ROBOT 4A]
Welcome!
[GROUP gasps]
Amazing!
This idea might actually work.
Everyone will be
talking about it!
People will come from all over!
Just to see our Buddha!
[KAZUSHI]
Are you joking?!
Come on Tatsuo, not you, too.
What the hell is this?
What did you think
you were doing, old man?
This is blasphemy!
[USHIMATSU]
What? I think it's unique.
How is it blasphemous?
Manoyama Wood Carving is
a traditional art form!
And as such it is protected
by the government!
Why don't you think
about it for a minute?
One of the conditions
for traditional art forms
is that they're
a viable industry.
At this rate it won't
be long before its
protected status as a
national art form is revoked.
Is that so?
Don't you have a
single ounce of pride?
[USHIMATSU] You can't make
a living from pride!
You idiot! That's precisely
what we've been doing!
I think you've mistaken
being proud for being loud!
Please, that's quite enough.
--What?
--I'm sorry.
This is completely our fault.
"Too wise to woo peaceably."
--[USHIMATSU] Say what?
--[CHITOSE] What?
It's from Shakespeare.
It's about lovers.
We're not lovers!
[door opens]
How'd it go?
He said it doesn't matter what
the Board of Merchants says.
We can continue the project
under his authority.
I can't decide if that
feels right or not though.
What's up? You ladies
get in trouble again?
What the hell?
Kabura Sushi Soda.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
How can you serve this stuff?
I just had a
disturbing thought.
In the end, was what we did just
like turning sushi into soda?
I have to go back.
I want to apologize
one more time.
[SANAE]
I'm so truly sorry.
But I hope you do
understand one thing--
that our efforts were
absolutely sincere.
We think Manoyama
wood carving is wonderful.
That's why we want
to promote it.
And as outsiders, we want
to give back to the town.
Just the same as you and Tatsuo.
All right, why don't you tell me
why you came to Manoyama?
Because...
I wanted to be
surrounded by nature,
and I wanted to be my own boss.
You sure you weren't
simply running away
from something difficult?
Running anywhere, am I right?
Didn't matter where.
I don't care to be
lectured by someone
who came here as an escape.
I chose to come to this
place with a purpose.
Unlike you two.
I'm sorry, but I don't
think that's fair at all!
Yoshino...
We've been working
really hard on this idea.
We've racked our brains
trying to think of ways
to get people excited
about Manoyama Wood Carving--
Sorry, but nobody
asked you to do that.
Let me ask you something.
What type of wood do you
think that is over there?
No idea, right?
And yet you assume
you're qualified
to talk about
Manoyama Wood Carving?
What a joke.
Thanks for trying back there.
But I think he
might've been right
about my running away
just to escape.
[YOSHINO]
What do you mean?
[SANAE]
In Tokyo, I worked overtime
late into the evening
every single day.
I'd stumble, exhausted, onto
the last train of the night,
only to squish myself back
on it the next morning
with everyone else.
On my days off, I was so spent
that I would just
stay in bed all day.
I got very sick and had
to check in to the hospital.
I went back too soon.
I thought things would
fall apart if I didn't.
Missed deadlines
and angry clients.
Those seemed like the end
of the world back then.
It was so silly, though.
I forced myself
to leave the hospital,
but someone had
been covering for me,
so everything was fine.
There was no reason
to rush back like that.
And that's when
I finally realized...
It doesn't always have to be me.
The world is perfectly
capable of turning on its own,
with or without my help.
Everything suddenly
seemed so ridiculous.
So do you see?
That's why I can't argue
with someone like Kazushi.
There's nobody to take
his place--he's the only one.
The only one that
can do that job.
But that doesn't mean--
[SANAE]
I can't do this anymore.
I shouldn't be involved if
I have no purpose
and I'm not putting
my heart into it.
You are!
You've been so invested in it!
[SANAE]
I'm sorry.
I know you're
determined to see this
through to the end, Yoshino.
But I can't.
I can't anymore.
[SANDAL] When life is hard
and you're feeling down,
take a deep breath,
and look up at the sky.
[SANDAL] Next time:
"The Budding Yggdrasil."