[EDITOR]
It's been so long.
Since the reunion, right?
Uh, yeah.
Things still all lovey-dovey
with that hairy man of yours?
Please. You know how it goes.
Our daughter is
the apple of his eye.
She's all he can see these days.
Her name is Himeno, isn't it?
Yes, though I'm
surprised you remember.
Guess you're not as
forgetful as you used to be.
So, tell me about her.
Does she take after her father?
Or did she get your looks?
Should I be concerned about
your interest in my daughter?
Huh? Uh, no!
I'm asking in a purely
professional capacity.
[NOZOMI]
Huh?
Hime?
Maybe, but she looks different.
[NOZOMI]
No, there's something sexy
about this girl that
Hime doesn't have.
[AKECHI]
Boo!
Ah!
What are you doing?
Jeez, someone's jumpy.
[NOZOMI]
Well, someone snuck up on me.
So, doing some reading?
[giggles]
[NOZOMI]
What are you laughing about?
Oh, you know.
Just thinking that you're
starting to grow up.
Little shota girl.
It's adorable.
[NOZOMI]
Don't call me a shota girl!
What are you even talking about?
[AKECHI] Your newfound interest
in fashion, of course.
Huh?! Uh...
Wait, that's not it!
Here, see?
Take a look at the cover.
Huh?
[NOZOMI]
Well?
Doesn't she look like Hime?
[AKECHI] Hmm...
That's actually her, isn't it?
Yeah, that's what
I was thinking.
[AKECHI]
On the cover of a magazine?
Way to go, Hime!
Is that a big deal or something?
[AKECHI] Uh, you're
totally kidding me, right?
That's the kind of thing
people dream about.
It's sort of a shame,
though, don't you think?
Why's that?
You realize she's going to be
on a totally different
level than us now?
[NOZOMI]
Huh?
[AKECHI]
I mean, she's a model!
That's gonna keep
her pretty busy.
I bet she'll have to go to
work right after school.
She probably won't have time
to hang out with you anymore.
You'll be all alone.
No, you're wrong!
[AKECHI]
I know!
Why don't you try
being a model, too?
That's crazy.
[AKECHI] I think there's
a demand for your type.
There's no way I could do it.
I don't know anything
about fashion.
[AKECHI]
That's easy to fix.
Come over to my place.
I can teach you everything
you need to know.
Everything.
I think I'm gonna pass.
Why? Come on!
I need a shower after
that look you gave me.
[AKECHI groans]
Okay, if that's how
you want to play it.
[NOZOMI]
Hmm?
[AKECHI]
Did you know that our school
doesn't allow students to work?
I heard there was a second year
who got caught,
and they were expelled.
Oh, dear. What if
someone finds out?
I might slip up
and accidentally tell a teacher
about Himeno's modeling
You're really evil.
You know that, don't you?
[AKECHI]
Heheeee...
Oh, wow.
You wear a bra?
You already knew that.
You've seen me
change in P.E. before.
I'm just going to
comb back your hair,
and then I've got
a wig for you to try on.
Perfect!
You're a precious little angel!
She is.
You're doing this
because you like to cosplay
not because you want to
teach me anything about fashion!
Yeah, so what?
Now, let's see how
this looks on you.
[NOZOMI]
Ugh...
Have you guys looked
through this magazine?
I mean, the pictures of
Himeno are pretty, and all,
but I don't get why
they have this spread
of an Antarctican snake girl.
I didn't really think
this was the kind of thing
snake people would read.
At least some
must if it's in there.
And "snake people"
is a derogatory term.
You should call them
Antarcticans.
Anyway, I'm not surprised
that spread is in there.
Magazines like
that are always careful
to treat all the races equally.
[NOZOMI]
I think I've had enough.
If you're just going to use me
as a dress-up doll, I'm leaving.
Aw...Hmm...
Heh!
[AKECHI] It's gotta be hard to
get letters of recommendation
after being expelled.
[INUKAI]
Play nice.
[NOZOMI growls]
[NOZOMI sighs]
Is something bothering
you, Nozomi?
You seem down.
Do I?
You look like someone
kicked your puppy.
Tell me something, Hime.
What?
Is there anything you've
been hiding from us?
[gasps]
This is delicious!
I'm glad we came.
[NOZOMI] If you eat
too many, you'll get fat.
Yeah, you're right.
Okay. See ya!
Hiding? What would I be hiding?
Oh!
[KYOKO]
This, maybe?
Oh, you meant that.
[giggles]
[NOZOMI]
Why didn't you tell us?
You know this is
a bad idea, right?
No, why's it a bad idea?
[KYOKO]
"Students are forbidden to work
while attending this school."
Does it really count if I didn't
get paid for doing it, though?
[NOZOMI]
Is that what matters?
I think it's about distracting
from our studies.
I was doing a favor.
The magazine's editor-in-chief
is a friend of my mom's.
Apparently, they have trouble
getting centaur models,
so she kind of
begged me to do it.
Yeah, there aren't all
that many centaurs around.
So, you're not a "model," then?
I wouldn't make it
a career or anything.
[KYOKO]
Why not?
Because it's against the rules?
[HIMENO]
Hmm...
That, too.
But also, because
I'd be embarrassed.
Plus, I'd have to watch
my weight all the time.
And, to be honest, the editor-
in-chief kind of scares me.
Aw, but you could
totally pull it off, though.
If the school rules
were different, anyway.
[HIMENO] I don't think it
would be a good fit for me.
Huh...
[KYOKO]
I dunno.
You seem like
model material to me.
You're super cute,
and you've got the height.
I bet you could be successful
if you worked at it.
Even if that were true, a
model's not what I want to be.
Well, what is?
[HIMENO]
Hmm... A doctor, I think.
You a doctor?
Sounds just a little scary.
That isn't very nice!
Remember there are dangers
to being a doctor, too.
[HIMENO, NOZOMI]
Huh?
Doctors get sued
for malpractice and stuff
all the time, you know.
I guess I hadn't really
thought of that before.
Okay, maybe I'd be better off
becoming a veterinarian instead.
[barks]
[HIMENO]
That's dangerous too, though.
I mean, what if one
of my patients bites me?
Besides, the only pets
I've had are fish.
[NOZOMI]
You could be a fishmonger, then.
Sell tropical fish and stuff.
[KYOKO] Fishmongers
sell fish for eating.
[HIMENO]
Tropical fish are tricky.
You have to watch the
nitrate levels of the water,
pH, temperature, everything.
[NOZOMI] Goldfish from festival
stalls never have their bowls
cleaned or anything,
and they live forever.
[HIMENO]
That's fine for them.
Algae produces oxygen
through photosynthesis,
breaks down their poop, and
even serves as food for them.
The problems happen
when humans clean their
bowls for easier viewing.
So, what, are you some
kind of fish expert now?
Stop!
[HIMENO]
If I did become a doctor,
I wouldn't necessarily
have to see patients.
There are plenty of doctors
who just do research.
My dad says that medical
research is a good field
to go into because the
budgets tend to be higher than
in other areas of study.
[KYOKO]
Wow, fascinating.
[NOZOMI] You've really
thought this through, huh?
I'm impressed, Hime.
Maybe we should start thinking
about our futures, too.
Well, I should, at least.
You'll probably be
taking over the dojo.
Nope, don't think so.
Never gonna happen!
Why do I feel like there's
something I'm forgetting?
[KYOKO]
I mean, can you believe that?
[HIMENO chuckles]
Oh, what do you need?
I know something I think you
would find very interesting.
Want to hear it?
[NOZOMI]
Hmm?
[INUKAI] Akechi is working
part time at a maid café.
[gasps]
Ah! No way!
[HIMENO]
Is something the matter?
[NOZOMI]
Uh... Nothing.
Thanks for that, Inukai.
You're pretty okay.
Don't mention it.
A little bird told me
that you're working
part-time at a maid café!
Yeah, sorta. You found out, huh?
[NOZOMI]
That's all you have to say?
Well, you had better
hope no one tells on you.
I trust that you're
not going to tell anyone.
After all, you're my friend.
So, are you saying
Hime's not your friend?
No, silly.
Of course, she is!
[NOZOMI growls]
[HIMENO]
Wait, what?
[KYOKO]
Brr.
It's freezing!
[sighs]
I'm a human popsicle.
[NOZOMI] You really are
a baby about the cold.
Well, I'm fragile.
[KYOKO] Not all of us discipline
ourselves with cold water baths.
Hey, shut up.
I don't do that.
[KYOKO sighs]
Talking about cold stuff is
just making me even colder.
[MANAMI]
Stop that. Get off of me.
[AKECHI laughs]
No way!
It's warm in here!
Honestly!
Hey, wait.
There!
Feel better now?
She's your girlfriend,
isn't she?
Do something!
I really would,
but she's a lost cause.
I'm sorry.
Oh! Hey, you three.
Yo, how's it going?
[NOZOMI]
Hey.
[HIMENO]
Nice to see you guys!
[KYOKO]
Good morning, I guess.
Ha! Come and
get in on this action.
It's so cozy!
They aren't yours to offer!
Aw...
Isn't this what
they're for, though?
[MANAMI]
No, they're for me.
Besides, the idea that
angelfolks' wings developed
as protection against the cold
is only one of many theories.
Nothing's been proven.
I know.
Some people even think they're
just decorative, like my horns.
They're warm,
though, so why not?
[KYOKO]
Lucky...
[NOZOMI]
Get a room.
[KYOKO sighs]
Nice and warm.
Hey, stop.
You're bothering Hime.
No, it's okay.
I don't mind.
Aren't you worried, though?
The other day you were
talking about being sent
to a correctional clinic.
[KYOKO] Yeah, that's
when we were talking
about getting up
on her completely.
I don't think I'll be arrested
for leaning on her shoulder.
'Kay. I'll join ya.
[gasps]
Oh, I take it back, this is
starting to get embarrassing.
Oooh. Nice.
Thanks for the show.
Lucky.
Well, I'm not
letting you in mine.
Who would want to
snuggle up to you, anyway?
You handle the heat just as
badly as you handle the cold.
Is there any
temperature you do like?
[KYOKO]
I have a delicate constitution.
This weather doesn't
bother you, Hime?
[HIMENO]
Hmm...
I don't mind the cold nearly
as much as you, I guess,
but I can't
stand the heat.
No wonder, given
how large your body is.
[KYOKO] Animals in polar
regions tend to be big.
[HIMENO]
Mm-hmm.
[KYOKO] It's an
evolutionary thing, I think.
The reduced ratio of
body mass to surface area
helps them maintain
a constant temperature.
Yeah, that makes sense.
[NOZOMI]
I think you lost me somewhere.
You're comparing
Hime to a polar bear?
[HIMENO]
A polar bear?
Those are kind of cute,
but also kind of not.
I have an idea, Kyoko.
[KYOKO]
Hmm?
Maybe it would help you to
forget how cold you are now
if you thought about sometime
when you felt warm
and happy instead.
Wait. What about
that time last spring?
That might work.
[KYOKO]
Hmm...
Am I melting?
I think I'm melting.
[SOLDIER B]
Hi there.
Stick together.
It's easy to get lost here.
It almost feels like
we're walking into
a jungle, doesn't it?
Except the jungle doesn't
smell so much like salt water.
Well, hello and welcome
to the fourteenth
High School for Waterfolk.
Aw, score!
We've hit the jackpot here!
Quit staring, you perv.
[KOMORI]
I can't!
They're all so hot,
and their racks are huge.
What are you talking about?
Boobs!
Mountainfolk have the
strangest bodies, don't they?
They're so different from ours.
That one in front
has such a flat chest
it's hard to
believe she's a girl.
Follow me, please.
[NOZOMI]
The way the merfolk are moving,
they kinda look more like
upright snakes than fish.
Maybe it's like treading water.
I mean, if they swam normally,
their textbooks would
get wet, wouldn't they?
They lowered
the water level today
to make it easier for you
mountainfolk to get around,
but if you want, I can show you
how we really swim later,
during our free period.
Hello!
Hi.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, same to you.
Hi--
[BOY A] So, you enjoying
yourself so far?
Uh...
[BOY B] Hey, how about we get
out of here during free period?
Back off, bro,
I got to her first.
What do you say I show
you around town later?
Nah, you should go with me.
I'm a good time.
Don't listen to them.
Kyoko seems to be a real
hit with the boys here.
She's a lot different than
the girls they're used to.
I can't help but notice
that you all seem
to have beautiful figures
and large eyes.
Uh, thank you.
[MANAMI] A lot different than
you see in paintings.
Huh?
Your tail is touching me.
'Cause you're taking
up the whole desk.
So, cute!
Look at him!
She's huge!
[MANAMI]
This should be interesting.
Hey you've got a pretty
unique look yourself.
I look "unique"? Like, how?
I promised myself
I wasn't going to ask,
but are you actually a boy?
A boy?
[GIRL E] Well, you look
just like the main character
in this book!
[NOZOMI]
No. I'm a girl.
[GIRL E]
Really? Let's see.
Hey! What are you doing?
Aw. I'm sorry about that.
What's going on over there?
All right, everyone,
it's time to begin class.
Settle down.
Quiet.
[MANAMI]
I feel like I've lost.
Very good.
Now then, all of you from
Shin Kanata High School
are probably...
And that was supposed
to be a good memory?
[NOZOMI]
Those guys were all over you...
...which doesn't happen often.
[KYOKO]
What was that last part?
And anyway, I almost ended
up with heatstroke that day.
It's probably a lot warmer
there than it is here now.
[KYOKO] Actually,
I heard it's cold in winter.
[NOZOMI] But they're
basically naked year-round.
How does that work?
[KYOKO] Their bodies
are built differently
than people of the other races.
They have to be,
considering they live
in water all their lives.
[KYOKO] Man, we're talking
about cold stuff again.
[laughs]
Sorry. Whoops.
No, don't worry about it.
You're going to
knock somebody over
if you're not more careful.
I know.
[NOZOMI] There's still
something overwhelming
about the merfolk to me.
Maybe.
But did you see how
he was carrying her,
like she was a princess?
[KYOKO] Your boyfriend
would need a crane.
[HIMENO]
Don't be mean!
I'm not that heavy.
I'd give anything to
have legs instead of fins.
[KOMA]
Don't say that.
Huh?
Don't you see?
You're not worth
any less as a person
just because you
can't walk on land.
It's all about
evolution, y'know?
What's wrong?
Is it a STEM major thing,
or a boy thing?
[KOMA]
Huh?
[PURPLE HAIR GIRL]
Hey, look.
It's Koma and Shizuura.
[snickers] You've got a pretty
raw deal, don't you Koma?
[KOMA]
No. I really don't, actually.
That's right.
He does this
because he wants to.
Oh, yeah? Somebody
sounds a little defensive.
Well, we don't
want to interrupt.
We'll just leave you two alone.
Why does he always go to so
much trouble for her, anyway?
Just because they've been
friends since they were little,
and she's kinda pretty
and has big boobs?
Probably. Sounds like
more than enough reasons.
An old friend,
pretty, big boobs.
[DOCTOR] Introducing
the Cyber Troll Company's
latest walking
assistance machine!
Climbs up and
down stairs with ease!
And, should you
lose your balance,
it'll always be
there to catch you.
Its sophisticated,
cutting-edge design
even makes surfing possible!
Doctor, some people believe that
allotting most of the equal
supplementary budget
to merfolk is
reverse discrimination.
Am I correct in assuming
you disagree with that?
I believe we must do
whatever is necessary
to achieve perfect equality.
We have made great
progress in that area,
but there is always more...
Here, I've got our drinks.
What's that you're watching?
A walking assistance
machine for merfolk.
I want one.
[KOMA]
That's expensive!
I could probably get
financial aid for it.
[KOMA]
Yeah. I guess.
Well...
[sighs]
You're right.
It's way too expensive.