[BOY]
Excuse me.
Yes?
Here you go.
I wrote this for you.
I want you to know how I feel.
Oh.
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Furukanata. Furukanata.
The doors will open on the left.
She ran!
No way!
--[NOZOMI] Hime!
--[KYOKO] Come back!
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
The eight a.m. local train
to Satose will be
closing its doors momentarily.
So, wanna tell us
why you bolted?
Well, um...
Out with it.
[HIMENO]
Umm...
[NOZOMI] Seriously, why'd you
run off without saying anything?
He seemed nice.
[HIMENO]
Uh...
[NOZOMI]
Come on!
Why won't you tell us?
You might want to try
ducking your head next time.
Hey!
Why didn't you at least take
the letter from the guy?
Well... I just...
I just couldn't accept it.
I've gotta know. Tell me now!
[HIMENO]
Uhm...
Stop asking me. Please?
'Kay, spill.
You're killing me, Hime.
Uh, it's embarrassing.
[NOZOMI]
So...
Why did you run away?
You're at home, and
no one's listening but us.
You can talk now, can't you?
Yep. She's right.
[NOZOMI]
He didn't seem like a bad guy.
Was it because
of the bald thing?
[KYOKO]
Actually, he wasn't bald.
He had a buzz cut,
and he looked like a jock.
I bet he's into sports.
Yeah?
Think he smells all sweaty?
[KYOKO]
He looked clean enough.
[NOZOMI]
Well, that's something.
In any case, I didn't see
a reason to run away.
There wasn't anything
wrong with him.
Then why run?
The truth is... I'm scared.
Huh?
Of boys?
[NOZOMI]
What? When did that happen?
You talk to Komori
and Nekomi in class.
Well, talking to them about
normal stuff isn't a problem.
It's just...
Huh?
Just what?
Uh. The thing is...
[KYOKO]
Wait.
I think I know what the deal is.
It's going out with
a guy that scares you.
So, is that what
you're scared of?
Oh! Wait!
It's sex stuff, isn't it?
What?
You think that's it?
[KYOKO]
So, sex stuff.
That doesn't really fit, though.
Hime isn't that type of girl.
Although, maybe it's
what comes after.
Are you afraid that you
might end up pregnant?
[KYOKO] Being a hybrid of
differently-shaped species
makes childbirth
tough for centaurs.
[NOZOMI] Oh yeah,
we had a lesson on that once.
[KYOKO] If pregnancy is
what you're worried about,
the government offers support
for that kind of thing.
[NOZOMI] You would
know that, wouldn't you?
So, is it pregnancy?
[HIMENO]
Uh-uh.
Really? It's not?
Will you just tell us already?
Okay.
[HIMENO] It happened when
I was in kindergarten.
[gasps]
[BRAT]
Is that what yours looks like?
[HIMENO]
N-No! That's a cow!
Are you going to have
huge boobies like that, too?
[sobs]
Oh, Hime.
So, that's what
you're worried about?
That you're gross down there,
like a cow or something.
Well, he was right
about the big boobs.
Quit it!
[laughs]
[sighs]
[KYOKO] Have you
ever looked at yourself?
Too scared.
[NOZOMI] That doesn't
give us much to go on.
It'll be okay.
I don't know if guys even
care about that stuff.
And why worry about it when
you're not dating anyone, right?
That's true, but if
I keep feeling like this,
how can I ever date someone?
[NOZOMI, KYOKO]
Hmm...
Yeah, I guess you've
got a point there.
[KYOKO] Well, have you
ever seen anyone else's?
[HIMENO]
Uh-uh!
Not even at
a public bath?
[HIMENO] I'm too self-conscious
at the public baths.
So, I just don't go.
[KYOKO]
And the pool?
[HIMENO]
Everyone covers themselves
when they change, you know?
[NOZOMI]
That's true.
Not sure why I asked that.
It's not like I've seen
anyone's before either.
Yeah, same here.
The thing is, you'll probably
always be worried about it
until you compare how
you look down there
to how someone else does.
Yeah! That's what I'm afraid of!
[NOZOMI]
I've got an idea.
Simple solution: I'll show you.
[KYOKO, HIMENO gasp]
Sorry. Show me what?
[NOZOMI] I'll show you
what mine looks like.
Kyoko will, as well.
Wait, me?
Well, what if I don't want to?
Why not?
Because, it's weird.
But we're her friends.
That has nothing to do with it!
[NOZOMI]
Okay.
You can look at mine, Hime,
and we'll check yours for you.
Then you can stop worrying.
[HIMENO]
Mm-hmm.
[KYOKO, HIMENO]
Ohh...
Uh! Your breath is tickling me.
It's prettier than a cow's.
Well, I'd hope so.
It's never been used.
Uh!
Hey!
[NOZOMI]
All right.
You're up next, Kyoko.
[whimpers]
No, don't.
Get back!
[NOZOMI]
Not a chance!
[KYOKO shrieks]
[NOZOMI] Oh, it's
hairier than I expected.
[KYOKO]
Stop looking!
Sorry. We had to even things up.
Okay.
[NOZOMI] It's time to see
what you've got, Hime.
[NOZOMI]
Here we go!
Sorry.
How do you take this thing off?
Hey. Done crying?
[KYOKO, NOZOMI]
Hmm...
It's pretty!
[KYOKO]
Sort of youthful.
[HIMENO]
Umm...
Haven't you looked long enough?
[NOZOMI] You can't see it
yourself, can you?
I'll get a picture, okay?
Now, say cheese!
Stop! I don't need one.
Ah! Hey!
You're totally normal-looking.
So, feel better?
Yeah.
[NOZOMI]
Uh-oh.
[HIMENO]
Hmm?
[NOZOMI sighs]
Come on, Kyoko.
I'm sorry, okay?
Hime feels better,
so it was worth it, right?
I mean, nobody got hurt,
so what's the problem?
It's no big deal.
Let's just forget it.
[HIMENO gasps]
[HIMENO]
Hmm...
So, uh...
[HIMENO]
Hmm?
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Furukanata. Furukanata.
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
The doors are now opening.
I have to go!
Hold on!
What's wrong this time?
Hime!
Wait up!
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
The doors are now closing.
[NOZOMI]
Why'd you turn him down?
You ran away
from the poor guy again.
Yeah, I did!
[HIMENO]
His letter was all stuff
about how "big" and
"beautiful" my breasts were.
[NOZOMI]
Guess we shouldn't be surprised.
[KYOKO]
That's all boys think about.
[HIMENO sighs]
[KYOKO]
So, the product here is?
Can we try a different one?
[moans]
Okay, how about this?
[NOZOMI]
Ugh...!
I just don't get it!
Yeah, well, keep trying!
We haven't even been
at it for half an hour.
[KYOKO]
Get back here!
Put the manga down.
Hey.
Come on!
Nozomi!
You do remember why we're here,
spending our Sunday
afternoon studying, don't you?
We're doing this to help.
Unless you want
to fail another test.
I don't know if this
is helping, though.
[HIMENO]
That tickles!
[NOZOMI]
I'm never going to be able
to memorize all these formulas.
I think your problem is
that you're looking
at this the wrong way.
Math isn't just
memorizing formulas.
You also have
to understand them.
To know not just what
they are but why they work.
Once you do that,
everything is a lot simpler.
You can work through
a problem knowing
what each step
means instead of just
mindlessly plugging
numbers into formulas.
Don't you get it?
I can't remember them,
let alone understand them.
I'm trying to help
because I know you need it,
but if you won't cooperate.
Hime, put her in a pinion
hold so she can't run.
Oh!
I'm on it!
Is this the right way
to do a pinion hold?
No, it's not.
[KYOKO]
It's good enough.
Are you ready?
[NOZOMI]
Uh...
For what?
Lots of math, English, science,
physics, and classic literature.
I'm going to drill them
into your bones.
I've got a treat.
Just say "ahhhh."
Ah...
[HIMENO]
How is it?
Chocolatey.
And good for your blood sugar.
Your brain uses a lot of energy,
so you've got
to keep it well fed.
At the rate we're going, though,
you'll never be ready
for the test in time.
[NOZOMI growls]
You know, maybe you should
be a little nicer to me,
considering that's
my chocolate you're eating.
[KYOKO] You got it from a
kid at the dojo, didn't you?
[NOZOMI]
Something wrong with that?
Nothing at all.
It's delicious.
Okay.
We've replenished our energy.
Now it's time for round two.
What?
[HIMENO]
Huh?
Haven't we done enough?
It isn't like I'm planning on
becoming a professor, you know.
I don't need all this math.
You never know what
you might need someday.
There have got
to be more important things
I could be learning
about right now.
What kind of important things?
Like how to use
Hime's legs like a pillow?
[KYOKO]
Quit sulking!
Listen.
Studying for the sake of
studying may seem pointless,
but we're all expected to
understand the fundamentals.
Once you've got those down,
you can figure out how to
apply them to your own life.
Well, that's what my
father says, anyway.
That sounds pretty tough.
Yep. To be totally honest,
I don't really get it, either.
But knowing stuff is better
than not knowing, right?
[NOZOMI]
According to my dad.
All you need to get by is good
looks and a smooth tongue.
[HIMENO] That's weird from
somebody who practices karate.
All the more reason
for you to study.
Your tongue certainly
isn't smooth.
I guess she's not done sulking.
Why are we helping her again?
Well...
Please don't give
up yet, Nozomi.
If your scores don't improve,
you could end up
failing the whole year.
And if that happens,
Kyoko and I wouldn't be in
the same grade as you anymore.
We wouldn't get to
hang out together as much,
and I would hate that.
Think about how much fun
we have going on field trips.
If you weren't on them with us,
they'd be so lonely.
When you put it that way,
I've got no choice.
Let's get to studying.
[KYOKO] We just want
what's best for you.
[NOZOMI sobs]
Hang in there. You can do this!
Get back to work!
[sighs]
Huh?
[NOZOMI]
Oh! Look! Over there!
What's up?
[KYOKO]
The sky?
[NOZOMI]
It's gone, but there was a UFO!
[KYOKO]
You feeling okay?
I'm telling you, it was there!
I'm sure you saw something,
just not a UFO.
[NOZOMI] I saw it clearly,
and that's exactly what it was.
[HIMENO, KYOKO]
Hmm...
You know all
kinds of stuff, Kyoko.
If UFOs exist,
what do you think they are?
[KYOKO]
Hmm.
Some say alien ships, or
weapons developed by the Nazis,
or vehicles that were created
by Antarctican snake people.
I'm not convinced, though.
[KYOKO] If they are weapons,
developing them
would require a ton of
resources and personnel.
It's hard to imagine that kind
of thing flying under the radar.
And if it were aliens,
surely the would've made
contact with us by now.
Okay, then what
about the Antarcticans?
[KYOKO]
Honestly, I'm not sure.
We don't know much about
their level of technology,
so it's easy for people
to make crazy speculations.
People who look like reptiles
but live in Antarctica
are inherently mysterious.
I do think it's likely they have
technology we don't know about.
Still, if they had the knowledge
and resources to develop UFOs,
they probably wouldn't
be fighting with America.
[HIMENO]
Hmm...
[KYOKO]
Fun fact.
Huh?
When snake people travel abroad,
they ride the Aztec
National Charter Planes.
Really?
So, does that mean they don't
have airplanes or anything?
Oh!
Wait a sec, didn't the Aztecs
have some kind of
snake-like deity?
[KYOKO]
Yeah, Quetzalcoatl.
He was represented
as a feathered serpent
and said to be a god
of learning and writing.
Some even thought
he invented the calendar.
The Aztecs were quite advanced.
[NOZOMI sighs]
[HIMENO]
Here, this should help.
We'll take a little breather
before we get back to work.
You don't believe
me either, huh?
Well, I didn't see
it myself, so um...
I think aliens
could exist, though!
[chuckles]
I know you're trying to be nice,
but that's not really the point.
[KYOKO] Okay, moving
on to potential energy.
Yeah, yeah,
whatever you say, Teach.
What're you looking for?
You keep staring up at the sky.
I dunno, I thought
I might see something.
This again?
Seen any more?
Not yet.
[HIMENO]
Nice day, huh?
[NOZOMI]
Yeah, sure.
[ANNOUNCEMENT]
Furukanata. Furukanata.
[KYOKO]
Oh, we're here.
[NOZOMI] Isn't anything exciting
ever going to happen?
[KYOKO]
Stop looking up while you walk.
You'll run into something.
[HIMENO groans]
Seriously, Hime,
do we need to put
a helmet on you?
[groans]
[passing helicopter]
Huh? Well, that's interesting.
You might just get your wish
for something exciting.
Like what?
Why do you say that?
Don't be obvious,
but see if you can spot
anyone besides students.
Huh?
[KYOKO]
See the bulge in his jacket?
He's a public safety official
in street clothes.
Whoa.
What's he carrying?
Jeez, don't be so loud.
And stop looking around.
So, what do you
think's going on?
There's that minister
who went to our school.
He came here before.
Except, wasn't he forced to
resign after that gaffe he made?
Maybe there was
a terrorist threat!
[KYOKO] These are some
serious security measures.
Could it have something
to do with what I saw?
The UFO?
Oh, hey, Shigetoki!
Yes, hello there, Milady.
[NOZOMI] Do you know what's
going on around here?
[NOZOMI]
Oh, come on!
Don't be stingy.
Heh! You'll find out
soon, don't worry.
Huh?!
[AKECHI] Did you see
those people outside?
[KEI]
Yeah, crazy, huh?
[INUKAI] I wonder what
they're doing here.
Oh, hey look.
[NOZOMI]
They put another desk in.
[HIMENO] Maybe we're
getting a transfer student.
[KYOKO] It might have something
to do with all this security.
You think they could be royalty?
That would be crazy.
Royalty or not,
there's no question some
VIP kid's enrolling here.
Why here, though?
This is an ordinary
public high school.
There's nothing ordinary
about this security.
Who do you think the new kid is?
[INUKAI]
A foreign exchange student?
[KEI]
I hope it's a girl.
Huh...
[NOZOMI]
Why does it matter?
[TEACHER] Class, we have
a new student joining us.
Please welcome
Queztalcoatl Sassassul,
all the way from Antarctica.
[SUU]
I'm a long way from home,
but I'm looking forward
to studying here.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[TEACHER]
I'm sure you all have questions,
but let's save them for later.
We've added a desk for you.
Why don't you take
a seat over there.
[SUU]
Yes, ma'am.
Now, Kimihara.
You'll show her
the ropes, won't you?
[gasps]