[gasp]
[CHIS gasp]
[CHIS]
It's a dinosaur!
No, she's not.
'Kay, so she's a snake, then?
[MANAMI] This is Quetzalcoatl.
She's an Antarctican.
[CHIHO]
Antarcti-- What?
Que-- Quet-- Quetz-- Quetz--
Quetzy?
[SUU]
Please.
I would rather you use my
given name, Sassassul.
Uh, how about "Suu"?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
So what does your
mouth look like?
Do you have lots of teeth?
[CHIS scream]
That was cool! Do it again!
Girls! Stop that.
Don't be rude!
I'm sorry about my sisters.
No. Please, it's fine.
I like that they aren't
hesitant to approach me.
It makes me feel
more comfortable.
[KYOKO]
Hello, little Sue.
Well, go on, what do we
say when somebody greets us?
Oh, sorry. Hi.
A little more soft-spoken
than her big sis, huh?
The Chisters take
after her, though.
No doubtin' that.
[SUU]
Can you please get down?
I'm afraid you'll
strain my neck.
[MANAMI] Do they take after
me? I was nothing like them.
I was so quiet, my nickname
was "the Doll."
[CHIS]
Hey, Sis, we're all sweaty now.
[MANAMI] Well, it's a good thing
we're headed to the pool, then.
[ALL]
Yeah! The pool!
[CHINAMI]
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's get going!
No running, you three.
[ALL laughing]
I'm so ready to get
some sun today!
There we go.
Good.
Look! I changed all by myself.
Yeah, you did great.
[SHINO]
Thanks!
[CHIS] We changed all
by ourselves, too!
Well, it's not as impressive
when you three do it.
[ALL]
Poo!
Come on, let's get
out there, huh?
Wow, there's nothin' there.
[SUU] My kind don't need
to nurse our young.
Besides, I could say
the same for you two.
To be fair, we're not
nursing now, either.
Yeah, that's right.
It gets deeper
toward the middle.
Here!
[SHINO] Hime, I can't swim
here. It's too shallow.
Yeah, it's hard to
swim with your hooves
touching the bottom of the pool.
Huh?
You coming in?
Well, um, I'm actually
terrified of water.
[KYOKO]
Oh.
Even when it's this shallow?
The depth isn't the
issue, unfortunately.
It's the water itself.
Being in it frightens me.
It likely comes from
living in a place
where falling into the water
means certain death.
[KYOKO] Don't you have hot
springs and stuff, though?
Bathing is not a
custom of our kind.
Without sweat glands,
it doesn't really work.
We do clean our
bodies, of course.
[KYOKO] I'm impressed you
made it across the ocean.
I don't have wings,
but there are other ways
of flying through the air.
[CHIHO] Come on,
snake lady! Time to get in!
Please, I'll just stay out here.
[SUU screams]
[KYOKO]
Dead yet?
I appear to have survived.
Mew.
Are you okay?
Mew?
So cute!
[CHIS]
Isn't she?
It's time for a
change of scenery.
We're gonna check out the
racing pool. You comin'?
I'll just stay here.
Can I go, too?
I wanna go swim.
Okay, why don't we
go together, then?
[SHINO chuckles]
[ALL laughing]
[ALL]
Huh?
Wait up! We're coming, too!
[MANAMI]
Uh.
Where do you think you're going?
What're you doing?
Don't be pervy!
[MANAMI]
I'm not being pervy.
You three can't go
to the racing pool.
[CHIHO]
How come Shino gets to go?
Because she's a centaur.
Besides, were you going
to leave Sue behind?
[ALL]
Poo!
[MANAMI]
Careful, keep making that face,
it'll get stuck that way.
[ALL]
That wouldn't be pretty!
If you want to
learn how to swim,
I'll teach you here.
[SUU] I'm staying in
the shallow pool, too.
[CHIS grumble]
[SHINO] They're really good
swimmers, aren't they?
[HIMENO]
Yeah.
Surprising for Kyoko.
Did you see that
mermaid? Cool, huh?
[HIMENO]
Oh, it's deep.
It has to be for the
diving boards, I guess.
Can we go to the other side?
We should stay here.
My hooves don't touch the
bottom past this spot.
You mean you don't
know how to swim?
Well, no, that's
not the problem.
It's just if I did go under,
nobody would be
able to pull me out.
Hey, you ever wonder how
mermaids get out of the pool
and onto the diving blocks?
They probably get a
friend to help them.
Wow, that jump was amazing.
I think everyone was too busy
ooking at her chest to notice.
Your hooves will touch
the bottom soon,
so stretch your
front legs forward
and just kick with
your back legs.
Otherwise, you risk
cracking a hoof.
Good, we made it across.
I'm getting tired,
so let's head back to
where the little Chis are.
[SHINO]
'Kay.
Practicing your kicks, huh?
[CHIS]
Meow.
Wanna go play a little more?
[CHIS]
Hmph!
Aren't you too busy learning
how to swim in the big kid pool?
Hey!
[SHINO]
Heads up!
What was that for?
Oops, I slipped.
Ha! You are going down now!
[NOZOMI laughs]
[NOZOMI]
Take that!
[CHIS]
Meow!
[BOTH laughing]
That's hot, so make sure
you blow on it first.
Yummy?
[SHINO]
Mh-hm!
Warms you right up.
Pools can leave you
feeling a bit chilly.
[MANAMI]
Uh-oh.
I think we've lost one.
I'm not surprised after
how hard they played. Huh?
Are you sleepy too, Shino?
Go ahead and rest.
Hey, no napping for you three.
[CHIS]
Why not?
Because there's only
one of me, that's why.
I don't have enough arms
to carry all of you.
Shino has one big sis
all to herself, though!
So how come there's
only one of you for us?
Yeah, shouldn't we
have three big sisters?
Don't be silly.
Think of it this way:
If you had three sisters,
you'd get three
times the nagging.
[CHIS]
That wouldn't be awesome.
[NOZOMI]
Well, today's special,
so go ahead and
sleep if you want.
Wait, you can't just
make that decision.
What's wrong?
They have three extra
big sisters today.
[CHIGUSA, CHINAMI]
All right! Carry me, too!
Yeah, sure, I don't mind.
I don't mind, either.
I used to help care for
my younger sister, too.
[HIMENO] I didn't know
you had a younger sister.
Yes.
We're all born of
the same queen,
so that means we are
all related by blood.
It's different than
in human society,
where families tend to have two
parents and a few children.
[NOZOMI]
Wow, that's really wild.
[SUU] Although, when I
speak of my younger sister,
I am actually referring
to a specific child
who I was responsible
for raising.
It's not exactly the same,
but has much in common
with your concept
of a younger sister.
Are you sure? It's kind
of a hike to our house.
Yeah. I don't think a little
walk is gonna kill any of us.
[MANAMI]
Uh.
I'd like to hear more
about how you raised
your younger sister sometime.
The kids aren't the only ones.
I'm getting sleepy now, too.
Too bad. We can't
carry you, you know.
Aw.
[KYOKO] Hey, eyes open.
You don't want to drop Shino.
Yeah.
[HIMENO yawns]
[HIMENO, NOZOMI]
Hm?
[chuckles]
We're gonna tell scary stories.
[gasps]
What do you mean, like,
the kinda stories with
ghosts and stuff in them?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
That's right.
Monsters, too!
[HIMENO yelps]
[NOZOMI]
That's enough outta you.
--[slap]
--[VICE PRESIDENT grunts]
Telling scary stories
in broad daylight?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
No way. It has to be after dark.
In fact, I was
thinking this Friday.
If that works for you guys,
I'll get permission.
[NOZOMI]
To stay overnight?
[VICE PRESIDENT] I figure we'll
wrap things up by about ten.
[KYOKO gasps]
[NOZOMI] Are you even
allowed to set this up
without asking your
shrimp of a president?
Well, you see, Nozomi,
that's the point.
You all are awfully impertinent
for underclassmen, aren't you?
Are we impertinent?
I think we're
perfectly respectful.
Anyway, I'm going to
need a firm commitment
from all of you first.
I can't have you backing
out after I invite Towako.
[NOZOMI] If you're so
desperate to do this,
why not just recruit Captain
Mystery Spot over there?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
It isn't his company I'm after.
Oh, I see now.
So that's how it is?
That's exactly how it is.
[NOZOMI]
Well, that clears things up.
[VICE PRESIDENT]
There's no chance she'll come
if it's just going to be
the two of us, you know?
She puts on a good face,
but I know she gets lonely.
If you'll all be there,
I'm sure she'll agree to it.
And it'll give us a chance
to get to know our
clubmates better.
Two birds with one stone.
I feel so used.
Inviting us for cover?
Not totally.
We can compile all our
stories into a booklet
and submit it as a
record of our activities
at the end of the year.
Think about it.
We'll get a club room and
a bigger budget for next year.
So three birds with one stone.
When did we say anything about
wanting to stay in the club?
I don't know. Might be nice to
have a room to hang out in.
[NOZOMI grumbles]
Still sounds like
a hassle to me.
I have to leave here,
go teach brats karate, shower,
then turn around and
come back to school?
[HIMENO] Come on,
we should support them.
[NOZOMI, KYOKO]
We should?
I mean, why not, right?
What can it hurt?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
Kimihara.
Huh?
Thank you!
[NOZOMI yelps]
You should keep your
hands to yourself
if you don't want another one.
I just expressed my happiness
a little too
eagerly, that's all.
[NOZOMI]
Not buyin' that.
[VICE PRESIDENT]
It's true, though.
I'll give you a hug,
too, to prove it.
So now you're sexually
harassing me?
Hey, one question.
Why not just ask her out
like a normal person?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
If I thought that would work,
I wouldn't be asking
you people for help.
And also, why scary stories?
That all you could think of?
It's this or a
mystery spot tour,
a power spot pilgrimage,
or UFO gazing.
A horror movie marathon
would be better.
So you're hoping this will
bring you and the club
president closer?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
Mh-hm.
Will you please help me?
Sure!
Are you sure?
You won't get scared?
I'll try real hard!
[VICE PRESIDENT]
So... I can count all of you in?
[KYOKO]
Fine with me, I guess.
[NOZOMI]
Well, if Hime's going to go.
[HIMENO]
I will if you all do.
[SUU] It sounds like an
excellent opportunity
to experience your culture.
[VICE PRESIDENT]
Awesome!
So everyone needs to come up
with about ten scary stories.
Overkill, much?
I'm excited to hear what
everybody comes up with!
And you really won't be scared?
I should be fine as long
as no ghosts show up.
[VICE PRESIDENT]
It's settled, then.
Be honest, though. You think
this is going to work?
The prez doesn't
strike me as the type
to be bothered by scary stories.
This might not go
the way you expect.
[TOWAKO]
I only believe what can be
objectively verified as truth!
[VICE PRESIDENT]
You don't know Towako that well.
I, on the other hand,
know everything,
including her measurements.
I like my chances.
[NOZOMI]
You're gross.
[DOG barking]
[HIMENO] The school is pretty
scary at night, isn't it?
[TOWAKO]
Yeah, kind of.
What?
I thought you didn't
believe in ghosts,
so what's to be scared of?
Ghosts or not,
this place is still creepy.
[NOZOMI]
Hey, you know what I heard?
This was a graveyard before
the school was built here.
I'm kidding. It
was just a field.
[HIMENO]
Jeez, don't do that!
[NOZOMI] You do hear a
lot of stories in a city
full of research schools
like this, though.
The one about the dog with
the human face started here.
I heard it used to be a
secret refuge for victims
of human experimentation
gone wrong.
Ah! That's too scary
to think about!
Enough of the dumb
urban legends already.
Especially since we haven't even
officially gotten started yet.
[NOZOMI]
Tatami mats?
[KYOKO]
This building must've had
a different purpose originally.
[NOZOMI]
Why candles?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
I figured why not go all-out?
No way I'm sticking around
for a hundred scary stories.
[VICE PRESIDENT] It's just
about setting the mood.
Come on, it'll be fun!
[HIMENO]
I'm already getting scared.
[VICE PRESIDENT]
All right.
I think we're ready
to get started.
'Kay. I'll do the first story.
So we all know this
town's origins, right?
How it started back in the day
as a college and industrial
research center?
Well, the events in the
story I'm about to tell
took place just after
the town was founded.
And so, that test
subject lingers still,
lurking down in the sewers.
Waiting there for the
next unfortunate victim
to come along.
And maybe... it will be you!
No, please, save me, Nozomi!
Stop laughing!
Trade seats with me?
[KYOKO]
Nah. I think I'll pass.
What's so scary about
an urban legend like that?
Well, uh, maybe because it seems
like it could really be true.
It's fitting for
a town like this
that it was about
genetic manipulation
instead of something like
demons or ghostly samurai.
[KYOKO]
Sometimes science is scarier
than the most frightening myths.
We don't know when we
might take it too far
or what the
consequences could be.
That's the point of the story.
[SUU] That we don't know
the limits of science
and testing them
could be dangerous?
[KYOKO]
Yeah, that's exactly it.
[HIMENO] Do you have scary
stories in Antarctica?
No, we don't.
You see, we don't
believe in souls,
or in supernatural phenomena.
In fact, we can't even
conceive of such things.
Of course, when I say that,
I don't mean to
deny your beliefs.
Nah. We don't really
believe in that stuff either.
Maybe not, but
it's still scary!
Now that I think about,
I do remember something.
When I was young,
I would walk only on the cracks
of the flagstone streets.
[SUU]
The one in charge of raising me
asked my reason for doing so.
[gasps]
You thought you'd fall?
[SUU]
Yes.
Rationally, I know that such
a thing isn't possible, but--
So basically, it's like this.
Antarcticans actually are
capable of being superstitious,
but they deny it because
it goes against the idea
that they are a civilization
founded on logic and reason.
Right?
[SUU]
That's amazing!
I knew I came to the
human world for a reason.
Well, thanks, but I don't
even know if I'm right.
Hey, we used to do
stuff like that, too.
Like when we would only
walk on the white lines
when we were using
the crosswalk.
Oh, yeah, we did do that.
And we made sure to stick
to the shaded parts
of the sidewalk, remember?
'Cause if you stepped in the
wrong place, you'd fall forever!
[VICE PRESIDENT]
Hey.
Didn't we come here to
tell scary stories?
[TOWAKO]
But science is more interesting
than stupid occult stuff.
Ha!
You just want to
change the subject
because you're
scared, aren't you?
[TOWAKO]
Uh! Hmph.
Well, okay, I can compromise
by telling a scary story
that also happens
to be scientific.
Plenty of people claim
to have seen spirits.
Soldiers, for example,
say they've seen Warring
States commanders
or fighters from the World War.
But there are never any mentions
of Kofun Period armor
or Bakumatsu rifles.
No primitive men
in furs, either.
And with animal spirits,
they're always things
like dogs or cats.
Creatures people everywhere
are familiar with.
No one sees Naumann's elephants.
In other words, no one
witnesses things
that don't exist in their
own consciousness.
That's why they're regarded
as hallucinations.
Except, I have a friend
who was walking by the sea
in a certain town one day,
and do you know what he saw?
[gasps]
[TEEN] Anomalocaris?
Aren't those extinct?
And it's walking.
How is that possible?
[TEEN] "A predatory creature
from the Cambrian Period.
It's believed they
swam in shallow seas,
but some fossils have been found
showing evidence of legs."
No way. Some of
them could walk!
[VICE PRESIDENT]
My friend saw something
that he never even
knew had existed.
So it must have been...
...a real ghost of
an Anomalocaris!
[HIMENO screams]
Your face is scarier
than that story.
Okay, I think I've had
enough of this for now.
I'm going to take a break
from these ridiculous stories
and use the restroom.
Does anyone want to,
um, come with?
[ALL]
Uh?
Stop! Don't go
thinking I'm scared.
I'll come if you want.
Me, too.
Seriously, I'm not
even a little scared!
I mean it!