[gasps]
Huh?!
--Huh?
--Hmm?
[KOMORI]
Ahh?
[gasps]
[NOZOMI gasps]
[HIMENO]
Huh?
[shocked noises]
[NOZOMI] We're supposed
to be rehearsing, here!
You didn't actually
have to do it.
Ah! But, well I...
It's just...
It was written
in the script, so...
What? It was?
[ALL]
Hmmm...
[KYOKO]
Uh-uh.
Where?
[HIMENO]
Um... Here, look.
[NOZOMI]
This was added by hand.
Not me. I had no idea.
Okay, someone must have
written it into her script.
But when?
They were just handed
out earlier today.
[HIMENO]
I don't know if it helps,
but I got my script from Komori.
[chuckles nervously]
[KOMORI cries out]
[groans]
[gasps]
Talk. Now.
[KOMORI]
Uh... Well, the thing is...
[HYAPPO]
Komori. Komori. Komori.
That's it.
Okay, the part of the prince
will be played by Makoto Komori.
[KOMORI]
All right! Yes!
[MANAMI]
That's enough. Sit down.
[KOMORI]
Yeah!
[MANAMI]
I mean it. Sit.
[KOMORI]
Here. I brought your script.
Oh. That's nice, thanks.
We're gonna knock 'em dead.
[HIMENO]
Yeah. Sure.
Seriously? Creep.
Don't forget our deal.
I want my foie gras roll.
[KOMORI]
Shut up, idiot!
Heh. Heh.
[MANAMI sighs]
So, it has come to my attention
that Komori used bribery
to secure his role.
He will no longer
play the prince.
I have decided--the part will
be played by Nozomi Gokuraku.
I don't wanna be
the stupid prince.
[screams]
[sighs]
The part was supposed
to be mine, not yours.
Such a pervert.
How desperate are you, man?
And as for you, Hime,
did you actually plan
to kiss Komori?
[gasps]
Well, I just, you know.
I thought it would be
okay if it was you.
Uh?!
Gettin' hot and heavy.
Love is in the air.
Please go away.
All right, people
it was just a kiss.
Back to rehearsing.
[KYOKO]
Oh? You wanted more?
Well, I, uh... Wha...?
[clears throat]
That's enough.
A kiss between friends
doesn't count as anything.
Let's get to work.
Yeah, okay.
By the way, I'm sorry.
No, don't.
There's nothing
to apologize for.
[NOZOMI]
Man, I'm exhausted.
Why did we have to pick a play?
A chorus or something
would've been easier.
I doubt that would have
been impressive enough
for our class president.
Come on. It is kinda fun.
To you, maybe.
Well you did get to
kiss Hime, didn't you?
Oh. I wasn't expecting that.
You're a good actor, Hime.
Have you done plays before?
Yeah, I have.
I played a princess
in middle school, too.
And in elementary school.
And in kindergarten.
Impressive what
about in the nursery?
Yeah, there, too.
I was my daddy's princess.
It's probably because
of my name.
[KYOKO] Nope, I'm gonna
go with looks and behavior.
I'd be fine just
playing Passerby A.
[KYOKO] Wow, so humble it
almost sounds like bragging.
Hey!
Things are really coming along.
We've got a costume
for you to try on, Hime.
[HIMENO giggles]
Wow!
It's amazing!
[AKECHI]
Better be. That was hard work.
The play's set in medieval
Scandinavia, right?
So, it's historically impossible
for there to have been
a centaur princess.
It could have happened
in Russia though,
so I used that for reference,
along with Central Asia
and the Near and Middle East.
You'll also see some
Baroque influence in the lace.
I guess you'd call it
Bourbon style?
Anyway, I guess the historical
inaccuracy bugs me a little,
so I just wanted
to add some...
[INUKAI]
That's gonna go on for a while.
Anything to do with costumes
brings out her inner nerd.
[AKECHI] ...everyone might
as well be on stage naked!
I'm not sure, though.
What?
[AKECHI] I thought I made
it on the larger side,
but it's pretty tight on you.
Ah!
[AKECHI]
Hmm...
[HIMENO]
Oh...
Hey, that looks great!
Way to go me!
[door sliding open]
[FUJIMOTO]
Mitama!
Is it okay if we
bring the set pieces in?
[MANAMI]
Oh, sure. Go ahead.
[FUJIMOTO]
All right, you guys.
Let's go!
[BOY D]
Coming!
[creaking]
[HIMENO gasps]
Hey, Fujimoto. One thing.
Huh?
I think we need to use
more braces on the platforms.
We tested them out, though.
They'll hold anything.
I mean, no one can be
heavier than Nekomi, right?
Uh...
[sighs]
Just do it.
You never know
what could happen.
It's better to be safe.
You're the boss.
[MANAMI] All right, we've
got costumes and the set.
Let's do a run through of
the whole thing, with feeling.
Oh, and skip the kiss this time.
[giggles]
Okay, everybody. Places!
[GIRL E] The play they're doing
has a real kissing scene.
[GIRL D]
Seriously?
Go on. You're gonna kiss, right?
No, they aren't.
Aww...
Perfect.
There's no stopping the
high school rumor mill.
[audience applause]
Right. We're up next.
Okay, let's carry in our set.
It's our turn!
I'm kinda nervous.
It'll be okay.
Hey, careful with that.
Don't worry. It's fine.
[ANNOUNCER] Next, we
have Class One-One's play,
A Dream Under the Midnight Sun.
Hey, good job.
You were a perfect queen.
Comes naturally, huh?
[MANAMI]
Shut up!
Don't you have something to do?
Nice work out there.
[HIMENO]
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let's nail
the final scene!
My love is true.
Even if Heaven and Earth
should fall, it will remain.
Hey. This is the part
with the kiss, right?
You think they'll
actually do it?
I guess there was no way
they'd do it for real, huh?
Yeah, that would be crazy.
[screams]
Help! Quick!
[NOZOMI]
Thank you.
[audience applause]
[NOZOMI]
The crowd loved the ending.
They said it was perfect.
Yeah, well.
I don't think the principal
was as impressed.
That's not surprising.
You two could've been hurt bad.
[NOZOMI]
Hmm...
Leave that to the president.
She'll smooth things over.
[GIRL D] Hey! I just wanna say,
you guys were great!
[NOZOMI chuckles]
Thank you!
[NOZOMI]
Hey, what's wrong?
Don't be shy.
We're past that now.
We are?
I'm glad you two are
having so much fun.
[NOZOMI] Sorry, I can give
you a kiss too if you want.
I'll pass!
[giggles]
[TEACHER] As I'm sure you recall
from your early biology courses,
modern day mammals,
birds, reptiles,
and amphibians have six legs.
It is widely believed
that this originated with fish,
whose pectoral, front ventral,
and rear ventral fins
grew over many generations until
they eventually became limbs.
[TEACHER] The genes
that determined the shape
of the pectoral fins
duplicated to form ventral fins,
which duplicated again
to form rear ventral fins.
Of course, in prehistoric times,
there were also
four-legged amphibians,
but they died out and
left no surviving descendants.
Most likely, extra limbs
evolved because six legs
were more advantageous than four
when it came to
supporting body weight.
Humans are the ultimate
product of evolution.
We can be broadly divided
into four different groups.
[TEACHER]
The first of these groups
includes the catfolk, the
goatfolk, and the fauns.
In the next group are the
angelfolk and the draconids.
The third group is the centaurs.
Weretigers were also included
in this group at one time,
but unfortunately
they are now extinct.
Finally, we have the merfolk,
though none of the students
in this room are
part of that group.
In the past, the differences
between the four groups
led to discrimination
and distrust,
often culminating in war.
Of course, had the four-legged
amphibians survived,
become the dominant race,
and evolved into humans,
things would be very different.
[TEACHER] There would
likely still be differences
in hair, skin, and eye color,
but nothing significant enough
to lead to serious
discrimination.
However, the idea of
a world in which humans
have just four limbs is absurd.
Something out of
a fantasy novel.
In reality, we must
remain vigilant at all times
if we wish to avoid the fear
and chaos of global conflict.
Some nations are still
plagued with violence,
while others strive for
the harmony that comes
from accepting each
group's differences.
We can only achieve
unity by viewing others
as neither greater
nor lesser than ourselves.
Therefore, equality is the key,
the virtue we must strive
for above all others.
All right. Now for
the national anthem.
[MANAMI]
Yes, ma'am. Stand.
[KYOKO pants]
Wait. Please wait.
[NOZOMI]
Huh? Huh...
Go faster.
Hey, go faster.
C'mon, go faster.
Can't you go any faster?
If you're about to collapse
after two kilometers
you should really
start exercising more.
I'm not a natural athlete, okay?
[pants]
You know, I don't get why we all
have to run the same distance.
Doesn't seem fair.
Mom and I run every day.
We do about twenty kilometers.
It's not so bad.
Why do you run so much?
A weight-loss thing?
Well, uh...
[NOZOMI]
You don't look that big to me.
Uh?!
[chuckles]
When centaurs gain weight,
we have a hard time
turning our bodies,
so we can't do stuff like
wiping our own behinds.
Oh, wow.
I didn't think you
could reach that far.
[HIMENO gasps]
Of course, I can!
'Kay, sorry.
I need... a break...
[NOZOMI]
If you don't get in shape,
you won't be able to
wipe your own butt.
I hate you!
No matter how much you eat,
you never gain weight, do you?
[KYOKO]
No, not really.
You're lucky.
[chuckles]
Hey. Hold on.
What was that chuckle for?
Well, your body's
nothing but straight lines.
Doesn't seem like something
to be jealous of to me.
I'll punch you, you jerk!
[NOZOMI laughs]
[KYOKO]
You!
[NOZOMI]
You'll have to catch me first.
[KYOKO]
Okay! I will!
[NOZOMI]
Good luck!
Hey, you're actually
running pretty fast.
[KYOKO pants]
I can't... Have to stop...
[HIMENO]
Are you okay?
Jeez, you look like
you're about to die.
[KYOKO]
And whose fault is that?
[HIMENO] Do you want me
to carry you on my back?
[KYOKO]
No way.
That's a terrible idea.
I'd be accused of discrimination
and sent to a
correctional clinic.
[NOZOMI]
That's a little dramatic.
It really isn't, actually.
In our country, centaurs
used to be warriors,
but in some places, they
were slaves used as mounts.
That's where most anti-
discrimination laws originated.
They take this stuff seriously.
Jeez, even talking like
this is probably illegal.
[NOZOMI] Anyway, once
you've caught your breath,
we'll take our time finishing.
No. I'm fine.
Go on ahead without me.
Don't worry,
it's not like we're trying
to get first place or anything.
I bet you that's what
Tama's going for, though.
Yeah, because being
class president isn't enough.
[NOZOMI] For the record, though,
if there was a cash prize,
I would ditch you
in a heartbeat.
[moans]
'Kay, let's go.
Huh? Already?
[NOZOMI] We still need to make
it back to school on time.
[NOZOMI]
Come on! Let's get moving.
We'll take it easy, okay?
Huh?
Hey, Hime?
[HIMENO]
Hmm?
If you try,
I bet you can go
really fast, huh?
[HIMENO]
Mm...
I can do a hundred meters
in nine seconds or so.
Is that fast?
[NOZOMI]
Yeah, crazy fast.
[HIMENO]
I can show you if you want.
There are no cars coming.
I'll just run to the stoplight.
[NOZOMI]
Okay, be careful, though.
[KYOKO]
Ready. Set. Go!
Oh, wow!
Too fast.
She's not gonna stop in time!
Hey! Stop, Hime!
[OLD MAN]
Hey, kid! Be careful!
I'm sorry!
[NOZOMI]
Hime!
Hey, are you okay?
Uh-huh.
[laughs]
It isn't funny.
You are crazy fast, huh?
You should run track.
I doubt there's anybody
who could beat you.
[HIMENO] Umm...
Yeah, that's not exactly true.
I actually gave it a try once.
[STARTER]
Ready!
[HIMENO]
Hey, wait!
Oh, right.
I forgot the heats
were divided by race.
Yep.
Okay, but what about a
sport like basketball?
[NOZOMI]
Uh...
Here! Pass!
Hime has the horsepower,
but she's not very graceful.
[KYOKO]
Too bad what a waste.
But still, it's gotta
be pretty nice
being faster
than most people.
You could be faster if you
worked out once in a while.
Hey, you've been leaning
on me long enough.
Huh?
Hey, wait for me.
Pick up the pace, you three.
We haven't got all day, here.
The lunch break is almost over.
Yes, ma'am.
[NOZOMI]
Wait, is that?
[KYOKO]
What are you doing on there?
Oh, hi.
Well, I didn't get much sleep
last night, so I'm worn out.
I hope you can make it, Kyoko.
We don't have any
more room on the bike.
Huh? Aww...
[COACH] All right, that's
enough chit-chat, ladies.
[AKECHI]
See ya!
[INUKAI]
Good luck.
[KYOKO moans]
Whining isn't gonna help.
Now, let's go.
[HIMENO]
Huh?
Hold on.
Hey, Nozomi!
You're going the wrong way!
The patrol's already
passed us, right?
So, let's take a shortcut.
[KYOKO] I guess you have
good ideas once in a while.
[NOZOMI]
Shut up, slow poke.
[HIMENO]
Is this really okay?
[KYOKO pants]
Shortcut or not.
I'm beat!
[NOZOMI]
Serves you right.
Maybe that'll teach you
not to slack off all the time.
[HIMENO] You can do it.
We're almost there.
[KYOKO moans]
[MANAMI]
Took you long enough. Hurry up!
Afternoon classes are starting.
[KYOKO moans]
Yay!
Whoa.
You look sick. Why?
What's your rank? Huh?
[KYOKO]
Oh...
Well, that sucks.
What did you say
about slacking off?
It's okay.
We can all study together.
You know you spoil
her too much, right?