It's kinda chilly down here.
Well, we are
underground in bikinis.
Are you doing okay, Suu?
Yes. I'm used to cold weather.
This doesn't bother me.
Right. Well, good. I'm glad.
Huh?
[HIMENO gasps]
[NOZOMI] This is a good way
to warm things up a bit.
Hey, shouldn't we be
staying focused?
I mean, what if something
jumps out at us?
[NOZOMI] Oh, something will,
right around the next corner.
Stop teasing! That's not nice.
Um, guys.
[NOZOMI]
See? Told ya.
[HIMENO]
Ah! It's coming this way!
[NOZOMI]
You know, it might help
if you would stop
with the screaming.
We got this, Suu.
Stay behind us.
Right.
[NOZOMI]
Hime, use your bow.
[HIMENO] Uh... but
won't we get in trouble
with the Animal Welfare people?
[NOZOMI]
It'll be fine.
Look at its face.
See? It's human.
They won't get mad
if you shoot a person.
[HIMENO] Um. Really? That
doesn't seem right somehow.
[NOZOMI]
Here it comes!
[TROLL roars]
[NOZOMI]
How did you miss?!
[HIMENO]
Ah! It ducked! I'm sorry!
My turn!
[NOZOMI]
Kyoko! Magic!
[KYOKO]
I'm on it. Just gimme a sec.
There. Done.
[KYOKO] Dora magura, goma
magura, sesame magura.
[NOZOMI]
Hey, what's the holdup?
Hooray, hooray!
Hooray, hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Uh, what're you doin'
back there, Suu?
Preforming a victory dance.
I thought it might be helpful.
More like distracting.
Upsy-daisy.
'Kay, got it.
Go on, fire. Do your thing.
Might wanna stand back.
You really think
this is gonna work?
Step back, and we'll find out.
[TROLL roaring]
[ALL gaspiing]
That's was awesome!
Yeah, I know.
Seriously, only two
gold? What a rip-off.
No, you've just been influenced
by the greedy capitalism
of the real world.
It seemed primitive,
but if it had money,
doesn't that mean it
was an intelligent being?
It didn't strike me as
being especially intelligent.
[KYOKO]
It's probably an instinct thing.
Like how crows
collect shiny stuff.
Did you see those claws?
It was obviously a monster.
[HIMENO]
Huh?
Which means that this labyrinth
is like a haunted house,
and the scary things
are comin' out to play.
I wish you hadn't said that.
I don't like haunted houses.
Right, because of
one bad experience.
You got spooked
and broke something
with your big butt, right?
How did you find out about that?
Oh, you know.
Well, let's go. Heh.
[NOZOMI]
Uh.
Looks like we've got company.
Hime, you can shoot
these guys, right?
Yep.
Kyoko, make with the magic.
I've got it covered.
[yells]
[NOZOMI]
Kyoko, where's that magic?
I'm working on it. Let's see...
Let me handle this.
[NOZOMI]
We don't need another dance.
Kay-su-yo-chi-no.
Eemay-ee-ko-chino.
Dako-pome-pino-peecone-pano.
Eee- dan-dee-kuh
Well, that worked.
But what the heck was it?
That was a sutra,
in the gods' language.
[NOZOMI]
Hm.
Aren't you supposed
to be a dancer?
I'm a priestess.
[KYOKO]
For what god?
I'm not sure.
[NOZOMI]
Only one lousy silver?
[HIMENO] Actually, there
are two more. Here, see?
[KYOKO]
Two, huh?
[HIMENO]
Not a bad haul.
[NOZOMI] We should be
pretty far down by now,
and we haven't run into
anyone but monsters yet.
[HIMENO] I wouldn't want to run
into anyone dressed like this.
It's kinda like
we're at the pool,
only with monsters
and weapons and stuff.
[HIMENO]
I wish I had your outfit, Kyoko.
[KYOKO]
Because of the cape?
Maybe you should've thought that
through when we chose our jobs.
[HIMENO] The mage's
incantations seemed like
they'd be too tricky
for me to manage.
I figured I could
handle a bow, though.
[NOZOMI]
Nah, it isn't that hard,
and I don't see how you could
be that much worse than Kyoko.
[KYOKO]
Hey, I beat that troll earlier.
[HIMENO yelps]
[NOZOMI]
What's wrong?
[HIMENO]
I stepped in something.
[BOTH gasp]
[KYOKO, HIMENO, SUU yelling]
Whatever this freaky stuff
is, it's not letting go!
Monsters are bad enough,
but now we've got this icky
green slime to deal with, too?
[SUU] Perhaps if we could
identify this substance,
we could find a way
to break free of it.
Oh my goodness...
Kyoko, use your magic
already! Make it stop!
[screams]
[HIMENO]
Kyoko, please!
There must be something.
Don't worry. I think
you're fine, actually.
We're fine, huh?
It doesn't look like
it's going to eat you.
Are you sure?
Who cares?! Just get
it off of us, Kyoko!
That stuff's harmless, really.
It'll just do sexy things to you
and put you in racy
positions for a while.
[yelps]
Oh, god! My armor!
I think it's melting!
[SUU]
When you say "sexy things,"
what exactly does that entail?
I'd like to help,
but the problem is,
if I use something like fire
or ice, it'll hit you too.
I don't know what to do.
Why don't you try salt water?
If this is a giant amoeba,
the osmotic pressure
should take care of it.
That sounds pretty scientific,
but I can at least
give it a try.
It'll be just a sec.
[HIMENO]
Hurry! Hurry!
[NOZOMI] Ah! Who said you
could touch in there?
[HIMENO]
Leave me alone!
[SUU] I don't know how much
longer I can endure this!
Okay, that oughtta do it.
Well, here goes nothing.
Piassa, selassa, regomar.
Splash and soak!
[ALL scream]
[sighs]
Huh?
That's a pretty sexy sight.
So embarrassing!
Indeed.
Kyoko, I'm not
gonna forget this!
[NOZOMI] All right, time
to fight the final boss.
[KYOKO] Really went
all-out, didn't they?
[NOZOMI]
Eh, who cares? Let's go!
Hey, anyone there?
[MANAMI] I'm surprised
that you made it this far.
Welcome, ladies.
I am the queen
of this labyrinth.
That's way too fitting.
Yeah, the "queen"
in which sense?
Wait, what do you mean?
That kind of queen?
[HIMENO, SUU]
What kinds are there?
[MANAMI]
Quiet!
Listen!
The paltry magic and
combat skills you possess
won't be enough to defeat me.
You must perform a task in
order to conquer the labyrinth,
and that task is to uncover
the queen's secret.
[KYOKO, NOZOMI]
Mm...
And if you give
the wrong answer,
you will be trapped here
for the rest of your lives!
[HIMENO gasps]
Okay, I think I've
got the answer.
Your secret is that
you pad your chest.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[MANAMI]
H-How did you know?
[KYOKO, NOZOMI]
Oh, please. It's obvious.
[NOZOMI]
Hey! Hold up!
[ALL yelping]
That's not good!
Let's get out!
[HIMENO screaming]
[SUU]
Please wait for me!
[KYOKO, NOZOMI]
Uhh...
So you wrote this thing
as some kind of
weird joke, right?
[AKECHI gasps]
[AKECHI]
That's what you think?
I like adventure stories.
They're amusing.
Totally!
There are more than
a couple problems
with this story, though.
For one thing, what good is
bikini armor gonna do anyone?
[AKECHI]
Hm.
Good point.
[KYOKO]
Hey, what're you looking at?
Hey, um... what's
everyone doing?
Ah, looks like the
favorite's finally here.
[KYOKO]
Okay, here we go.
And... begin!
Sorry, but I work out these
muscles every single day.
I won't lose to someone
who's not even in a club.
Done, and the winner
is the class prez.
Ow, that really hurt.
How the heck did you
get so strong, anyway?
[chuckles]
[MANAMI] My muscles get
plenty of workouts.
Yeah, fair enough.
'Kay, time for the next match,
and remember, girls,
no cheating.
[KATSURA gasps]
[KATSURA whines]
[NOZOMI] Arm wrestling is
about reading your opponent.
Just watch her very closely.
Right. I will do my best.
[SUU]
Stay calm and watch her closely.
[AIKOU] Man. Jeez.
She's really staring.
[NADE]
Let's have a fair fight.
Okay, ready. Let's wrestle!
Now!
[SUU gasps]
And the winner of this
match is Aikou!
[AIKOU cries]
I didn't do too well.
[NOZOMI]
Honestly.
[KATSURA]
Hey, you're up next, Hime.
Okay.
[HIMENO] Why is everybody
taking this so seriously?
Okay, grab hands.
I bet it'll be Princess.
[OMAKI]
Fuku's tough, too, though.
She's one of the top five in
the prefecture in shot put.
[FUKU]
Man, her hands are big.
Let's have a fair fight.
Okay, ready. Let's wrestle!
C'mon.
[OMAKI] Check out Hime.
She's as strong as a gorilla.
[HIMENO]
Hm?
There!
Owie!
[GIRLS grumble]
[HIMENO]
Aw, I guess I lost.
Huh?
[NADE]
Do-over. That one didn't count.
She's right! Be serious, here.
[HIMENO]
I'm being serious, really.
Let's up the stakes
a little bit.
If you lose again,
you'll have to pay the price,
by presenting your
breasts for verification.
[HIMENO]
Uh, "verification"?
That's right, a very up close
and personal assessment
to determine whether
or not they're real.
No way!
I can tell you right
now: They're real.
[NADE]
Uh, let's start again.
Let's have a fair fight.
Okay, ready, and let's wrestle!
[FUKU yelps]
Princess is the winner
of the rematch!
Sorry. Are you okay?
[FUKU] Aww... I lost.
After all that training.
A bet is a bet.
Do with me as you will.
[HIMENO] Uh! Why are you
taking your clothes off?
[KATSURA]
You weren't part of the bet.
Oh, okay.
Jeez!
How did we get
paired up together?
You look like you're
about as weak as a kitten.
Well, you look weaker.
[NADE]
Winner!
[AKIRA grunting]
I gotta say, Akira.
You've got decent reflexes,
but when it comes to strength,
you're pretty pathetic.
Maybe if you helped your
mom out every now and then.
[AKIRA] Shut up.
You don't know anything!
[NOZOMI]
And down you go.
[KATSURA]
The kendo club member lost!
[FUKU]
And the tea club member won!
Whew, this is exhausting.
So, uh, why are we doing this?
[KYOKO]
Hm?
[KATSURA] Hey, come on,
Princess. You're up.
[HIMENO whines]
Go get 'em, Hime.
I'm sorry!
And it's over!
All right, everyone, the winner
of this match is Nozomi.
Aw, man, I lost.
I was doing so well.
She beat you, too,
so I guess it's okay.
This is dumb. Who really
cares about arm wrestling?
[AKECHI] Okay, we're
down to our four best!
Go Michi!
[KYOKO]
No favoritism.
Well, we've known one
another or many years now,
but it looks like it's finally
time to settle the score.
Jeez, it's an arm
wrestling tournament.
We're not goin'
into battle, here.
Got anything, Princess?
still don't understand
why we're doing this.
[INUKAI]
Uh?
[SATOU]
I'm surprised no one's left
from any of the athletic teams.
[OMAKI]
Well, Hime and Nozomi
are both involved
with local dojos.
Wait for my signal.
No false starting.
Ready.
Go!
Seems I'm not the only one.
You're taking this
seriously, too.
Yeah, well I appreciate
a good competition
as much as you do.
[KATSURA]
The winner is Mitama!
Man, my hand's gonna be
sore for like a week.
We build strength differently.
I guess this means
child-rearing beats karate.
[KYOKO]
You know what they say,
"no one's stronger
than a mother."
Not that she is a mother.
[NADE] All right, Inukai,
Princess, come on.
You're up next.
Okay, I'm coming.
[NOZOMI]
You got this!
To warn you,
I don't think this is going
to be a close contest.
I guess we'll find out, huh?
I know about Princess
and her archery,
but what about Inukai?
How'd she get so strong?
Well, she's pretty tall,
and she was into sports
in middle school, too.
Really, her strength
comes from love.
From love? So what
are you saying?
You guys get cozy
ekiben -style every day,
and that's why
Inukai's so strong?
Ekiben ? The train
station bento boxes?
Who doesn't love ekiben ?
You are so dirty.
Please, you're the one
with the dirty mind, here.
Uh, just ignore her.
[NADE]
Here we go.
Okay, ready. Let's wrestle!
[INUKAI gasps]
Princess is the winner.
You are crazy strong, huh?
Sorry about that. You okay?
Oh, well, looks like
your love lost.
I wonder if I should be
doing something differently.
Take it too far and
you'll just look silly.
[NADE]
Time for the final round!
Do you need a break?
No thanks, I'll be fine.
I still don't know why
we're doing this, though.
This may be a game, but
it's one I will not lose.
Tama, you sound really
scary sometimes.
[NADE]
Let's have a fair fight.
Okay, ready. Let's wrestle!
Sorry!
[gasps]
[STUDENTS gasping, applauding]
[NOZOMI] I guess no one
can beat Hime, huh?
[KYOKO]
Looks like it.
Hey, Tama, are you okay?
[MANAMI sighs]
I feel like I let down my
little sisters by losing to you.
[HIMENO]
Uhh...
Well, you know, I
spend a lot of time
carrying Shino around.
I think she probably
weighs three times
as much as the Chisters.
Three times, huh?
That gives me an idea
of how much you weigh.
No, don't tell anyone!
I mean it. I'm serious! Okay?!
You won't tell anyone, right?
[HIMENO]
Also, why are we arm wrestling?