[KYOKO, NOZOMI]
Oh, wow.
So that's what
yabusame looks like.
[KYOKO, NOZOMI]
Uh?
[gasps]
That was painful.
[SUU]
Was that a failed attempt?
Yeah, total fail.
[chuckles]
[AYAKA] Are you losing
your edge already?
[HIMENO yelps]
Careful! It's dangerous
to shoot past people!
[AYAKA]
I know. I'm sorry.
No, I take it back!
[HIMENO]
Huh?
It looked like you
were slacking off,
so I thought I'd give
you a wake-up call.
[KYOKO]
Uh, Hime?
Oh, right, I'm sorry.
You haven't met.
This is Ayaka Wakamaki.
She's in middle school.
Hello.
Despite the little
prank she just played,
she's normally a
well-behaved serious girl.
She's great at yabusame
and regular kyudo.
Stop it. I don't need
you to talk me up.
You say I'm good?
You're the one who won the
yabusame meet last year.
[HIMENO]
So rebellious.
[AYAKA] But I'm not going to let
that happen again this year.
Okay.
Sure. We'll both do our best!
[AYAKA grumbles]
I need to go.
If you're coming to
the meet to support her,
I promise that you
will be disappointed.
I meant it when I said I
was going to win this year.
I hope she'll at least put
up a good fight, though.
Goodbye.
[HIMENO]
Uh.
What is it?
Well, I was just wondering,
how did the kyudo tournament go?
I placed third individually.
I won't be advancing
to the nationals.
In the team competition,
I didn't even graze the target.
And that means I have extra
motivation to beat you,
so I can end my middle
school archery career
on a high note.
You had better
bring your A game!
What's her deal? That is one
high-strung middle schooler.
Yeah. She gets like that.
It's probably her biggest
weakness as a competitor.
[HIMENO] Last year, I wanted to
see if I could do something
to help her relax.
[grunting]
[HIMENO]
Ayaka, over here!
Ah! Boo!
You feeling better now?
Did you come here just
to make fun of me?
Thanks, my concentration's
totally shot.
[NOZOMI]
"Boo"? Seriously?
Shino thinks it's funny
whenever I do it to her.
If Ayaka was five years old,
maybe she would, too.
Anyway, ever since then,
I've gotten the
feeling she hates me.
She came over here just
to get your attention.
That doesn't seem like hate.
Actually, I'd say
she likes you.
You think so?
That's the impression you get?
[KYOKO, NOZOMI]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
As a matter of fact,
I have a fantastic idea.
Just, you know, a way you
can get her to relax.
Yeah? Really? What?
Tell her if you then...
I don't know. Are you
sure that would be okay?
[KYOKO]
Absolutely. Trust me.
[KONATAMOREI]
Hey.
[HIMENO]
Hi, Konatamorei!
You've wasted enough
time on girl talk today.
Back to practice.
'Kay.
I don't think you girls
are ready for yabusame ,
but maybe you could
always give kyudo a try.
[HIMENO] It was cool of you to
stick around during practice.
[KYOKO]
No problem.
[NOZOMI] Yeah, we actually
had a pretty good time.
[SUU sighs]
I always thought archery
was fairly straightforward,
but it's much more
difficult than it looks.
Japanese archery especially.
You're obviously
quite good at it.
Any particular reason
you chose archery?
Uh... I guess I got into it
because my mom told me to.
She said something
about how my grandpa
would give her a hard
time if I didn't at least try.
Hey, did you know, originally,
it wasn't about the sport,
but for matchmaking.
A way you could meet
potential mates.
Having access to a practice
space, good equipment,
and plenty of leisure time
to hone one's skills
was seen as proof of both
wealth and physical fitness.
[KYOKO] Since there
aren't that many centaurs,
practicing archery
was a practical way
to meet a husband or
wife of the same race.
And to facilitate reproduction?
[KYOKO]
Well, putting it that way
might be a little too direct.
I didn't realize the word
"reproduction" was an obscenity.
I felt certain it was
a technical term.
[KYOKO] It depends on
the time and place.
Uhh...
Oh, for me, it's not about that.
I mean, um, the
reproduction thing.
No babies yet!
So, you're only in it
to find a husband, then?
No way.
I think I'm a little young
for that, don't you?
Although, I wonder what
it's like for Ayaka.
I think she's from a
pretty wealthy family.
[KYOKO] Well, she's not old
enough to get married.
That doesn't rule out an
engagement, though.
Ah...
[HIMENO, NOZOMI chuckle]
[SUU]
Hm?
An Antarctican?
Wow.
Why's she here?
Hello. Good to see you.
Yeah, you too.
Good afternoon.
Hiya.
[NOZOMI] What's our
vice-president doing here?
Sorry, who are they again?
They're in the same
class as Komori.
Nope, that's still not
ringing any bells.
Remember the girl with
the pretty red hair?
They're probably
here to see her.
[SHOUJOU]
Gotcha.
[GUY A]
Oh, are you friends of Rei's?
[GIRL A]
That's cool. Have a good time.
That was kinda weird, huh?
Par for the course.
I was wondering where you
were. Come over and say hi!
Hey.
Oh, hello, girls.
Hi, Ms. Kimihara.
Hi, how are you?
An Antarctican?
[KYOKO]
Who's this?
Her name is Maki.
She's a friend of mine
from kindergarten.
[KYOKO]
Nice to meet you.
Hey, is that a monster?
Don't be mean. Of course
she's not a monster.
She's Suu.
[KYOKO]
Lookin' pretty sharp there.
[chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER]
Participants, please assemble.
Oh, I have to go.
See you later. Have fun!
[SHINO]
Good luck out there, Hime!
[NOZOMI]
Go get 'em!
Let's all go cheer for
her together, okay?
Scary monster!
[SHINO] Don't worry. Big sisters
Kyoko and Nozomi are here.
Besides, she's not a monster.
It's true. I would
never hurt anyone.
[SHINO]
Just give her a chance.
Uh, hey. Go talk to them.
Why me? You go.
Talking to high school girls
isn't really my specialty.
It's all right. I promise
Suu's completely harmless.
Sure, she's harmless,
but what about me?
Oh, wow, your big cousin is
so good, she hit every one!
That wasn't too bad.
[HIMENO]
Hm? Thank you.
[ANNOUNCER]
Next up, Ayaka Wakamaki.
[AYAKA]
I'm up. I have to go.
Could you wait
for just a second?
[AYAKA]
What now?
Are you going to say something
to distract me again?
No.
Then what do you want?
Why don't we make a bet?
To shake things up.
Well, that does
sound interesting.
Yeah, I thought you'd agree.
Say you want to make a
bet on the competition.
Right.
Tell her if you lose,
then you'll...
I'll go out on a date with you.
What? Are you kidding me?
Please! Stop messing around.
Jeez, she doesn't
look so good.
[AYAKA] Where would we go?
What would I wear?
No. I can worry later.
First, I have to beat her.
[HIMENO]
Sorry!
Where have you been?
Do you know how late you are?
There's so much I
have planned for us!
Come on, let's get going.
[KYOKO]
Why are we following them?
[NOZOMI]
Because it's fun?
I think we've been spotted.
[NOZOMI, KYOKO groan]
[chuckles]
[NOZOMI] It's your fault
she caught us, Kyoko.
[KYOKO]
Huh? How's it my fault?
[SUU]
Perhaps it was mine.
Are we going to
keep following them?
[NOZOMI]
Yeah, of course, we are.
[KYOKO]
No, we aren't.
[CARPENTER A]
Hey, take that over there.
I thought this was where
it was supposed to go.
Nope, whoever told
you that was wrong.
[CARPENTER C] If you've got a
sec, can you give me a hand?
[CARPENTER D]
Sure, no problem.
[CARPENTER C]
Thanks, man, I appreciate it.
This is it.
You gotta be kidding. Seriously?
Pretty awesome, huh?
Yeah, that's for sure.
How did you score a
magazine like this, though?
I didn't think they were
even sold in ocean towns.
My cousin's the one
who got it for me.
He's a competitive swimmer
in a land-bound town
so he has access to this stuff.
Lucky.
Hey, watch it!
What's your problem, huh?
[MIURA]
You know what the problem is.
You shouldn't be looking at
naughty magazines out here.
Honestly, you know
better than that.
[TEEN B] This is a perfectly
wholesome publication.
Then why did you look so excited
when you were reading it?
[TEEN B, TEEN A]
Um...
I don't get what
the big deal is.
You guys are surrounded
by boobs all day.
Why do you need to see
them in magazines, too?
It's simple.
Sometimes it's what you can't
see that's more exciting.
[TEEN A] You girls wear
swimsuits when people
come here from the
mountains, right?
[TEEN A]
Covered or not,
those guys were totally
staring at your chests.
[FUKAMI] So do you like
it when I do this?
[TEEN B, TEEN A]
Nope, already seen 'em.
Your choice of reading
material aside,
you're also slacking off on
the festival preparations.
We were just taking
a short break.
Ugh.
[TEEN B]
Hey, Eri.
[ERI]
Uh.
Hello.
[TEEN A, TEEN B gasp]
[MIURA] So you're the priestess
in the festival today?
[ERI]
Oh, yeah.
[BOTH chuckling]
Quit it!
You two stop ogling her chest!
Well, I should go now.
Good luck out there.
See ya later.
So hers do it for you, then?
[TEEN B, TEEN A]
Yeah, I guess.
[TEEN B] It's the way she acts
all embarrassed about it.
[TEEN A] You can tell
she was raised on land.
[BOTH chuckling]
Ugh. You guys are hopeless.
[sighs]
Just forget about it. Let's go.
Okay. See ya.
For a second there, I thought
we had a boy for a priestess.
That's sexual harassment.
I guess they raise kids pretty
strict on land, don't they?
The ocean waves must
be tiring you out.
Just rest up there for a bit.
You see our god
Dagon there, yes?
And you know your role
is to offer a song of
celebration to him?
I do.
[OLD MERMAN] It's not
something to take lightly.
The health of our ocean and
the fortune of our village
will depend on your song.
[OLD MERMAN]
The size of the audience
is an important factor, as well.
If it helps, think about it
as one of those concerts
you do all the time.
It's not really that different.
Well...
[OLD MERMAN]
Hm?
I may be a well-known singer,
but I'm not that popular.
This is the largest audience
I've had. Probably ever.
[OLD MERMAN chuckles]
[OLD MERMAN]
All right.
Well, then. You ready?
[ERI]
Yes.
[singing]
[gasps]
Just keep going.
[OLD MERMAN] It's a man-dolphin.
A messenger to the god Dagon.
It showed itself because it
approved of your song.
[ERI singing]
[DOLPHIN calling]
Hold on, what happened?
Why is the dolphin
swimming away?
[OLD MERMAN]
Hmm...
[TAGON]
I am the god Dagon.
Hear my words, humans,
and obey me.
Is that actually a real god?
Absolutely not.
That would be impossible.
We need to go!
It doesn't seem to
be pursuing us.
So that wasn't the physical
incarnation of the god Dagon?
[OLD MERMAN]
No.
Our god is the stone statue
you saw under the water.
No living incarnation exists.
That thing was an imposter.
But if there's no living god,
then what was the
monster we saw?
[OLD MERMAN]
Some kind of robot, perhaps?
A previously
undiscovered species?
A prop planted by a TV station?
A government experiment?
I honestly have no idea.
[OLD MERMAN] And when you
don't know what's going on,
it's usually best to flee.
Now, let's hurry.
We need to get back to the beach
and notify the Coast Guard.
[HIMENO]
Huh? A real god?
That's what I heard.
[NOZOMI]
Those don't exist, though.
Could it have been some kind
of mythical creature, maybe?
Or, uh...?
Oh! Let's ask the pro.
[MANAMI]
Mm.
[sighs]
I'm no pro.
Just because my family
happens to run a shrine,
that doesn't make me a
theologian or a shaman.
You don't think
they exist either?
[MANAMI]
Well, gods are just...
Okay, theology 101: What
does the word "god" mean?
How would you define it?
As a product of
people's imaginations!
What makes you so sure?
Have you forgotten the
source of our income?
Uh, Prez?
Of course gods exist.
Our shrine's god is a
true miracle worker.
It brings good health,
safety, increased beauty,
household harmony, and-most
effectively-academic success.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, you're second
in our grade, right?
Nice sales pitch.
Mew.
[ZASHIKI whining]
[growling]
[MANAMI'S DAD]
Hm?
Hey, Sue, are you
playing by yourself?
No, silly daddy, with my friend.
[MANAMI'S DAD]
Uh.
Okay, then, you two
have a good time.
Ah! I can't believe
I lost again!
[ZASHIKI yells]
I want a rematch! We're
playing one more game!
Okay.