[teacher] Congratulations,
everyone.
[adult Satoru narrating]
In 1988, the first time
I lived it,
Kayo Hinazuki
and Aya Nakanishi disappeared
and their bodies
were found later.
I was too helpless
to save anyone.
I tried hard to forget,
and I did.
But in the end, I had
a big gaping hole in my heart.
[teacher] These past six years,
we've experienced success
and failure,
happiness and sadness.
Good or bad,
the experiences we share
fill a void
we all have inside of us.
Everyone. Even me.
So keep filling it,
and you'll enrich your life,
and others' too.
That’s what life's about.
Never forget that.
[theme song plays]
[man singing in Japanese]
[Satoru] Uh, hey there.
[Aya] Who are you?
‐[Satoru] I'm Satoru Fujinuma.
‐[Kenya] I'm Kenya Kobayashi.
‐[Hiromi] I'm Hiromi Sugita.
[Aya] Have we met before?
[Satoru] Uh, you're
Aya Nakanishi.
I heard you're good at piano.
[Aya] Yeah, I guess.
So, did we meet
in piano class?
Well, actually, no.
So, anyway, what you reading?
[Aya] Oh, this? Shakespeare.
"King Lear." I've only read
"Romeo and Juliet."
[Aya] Reading this stuff
and playing piano
are my parents' idea.
[Kazu] I can't hear
what they're talking about.
Maybe we should try
and get a little closer.
Wait, now I remember where
I've seen you before.
You're the kids who are always
sneaking into that old building.
Aren't you?
Darn it. So much for having
a secret hideout.
Hideout? That's so childish.
‐[gasp] You...
‐You shouldn't call it childish.
Yeah, well, the only ones
who sneak around building forts
and secret hideouts
are little boys.
I bet you like playing
superhero too.
Don't make fun of superheroes!
‐[Hiromi] Easy, Satoru!
‐[Aya] Nice meeting you,
but I have to go now.
Bye, kids.
[Kazu] Hold up!
[boys] Kazu?!
‐What do you want?
‐A hideout...
is totally macho!
Uh...
‐[laughs]
‐You should come
and see it sometime.
You'll get what I mean.
[Aya] You're a bunch
of weirdoes!
[Kenya] She’s childish.
[Osamu] You were so rad
yesterday!
[adult Satoru thinking]
It's my gloves,
right where I left them
18 years ago.
‐Leveling up's
a pain in the nuts.
‐That's what makes games fun.
Hey, Satoru, Aya's gonna be
at the park soon,
so maybe we should
start heading over.
It's cool.
I can see the bench from here.
OK.
[adult Satoru thinking]
Yesterday was a wash.
I gotta figure out
how to get close to her.
[bam!]
All right, I'm here to see
this macho hideout of yours.
Um... thanks for coming, Aya.
Can you stay awhile?
Mm‐hmm.
‐[girl 1] See you.
‐[girl 2] Bye‐bye.
[humming]
You off to see Aya again?
[Kazu] Yep. We'll cruise by
the hideout later.
Well, guys, see you then!
‐Later days, teach!
‐"Goodbye" is more proper.
I can't picture Aya
and Kazu liking each other.
Yeah, me neither,
but the good thing is,
she's always got
someone with her now.
[Satoru] Mm‐hmm.
Um, you guys, I...
I just wanted to say thank you.
‐Why?
‐I think it's awesome
how you're going around
making sure
none of us are alone.
Both of my parents work,
and nothing felt worse
than me getting home
and the house being empty.
It's pretty awesome how you kept
Kayo and Aya and me from being
alone all the time.
So thank you.
[giggles]
Hey, guys!
We going to the hideout or what?
I'm getting tired of waiting.
‐What's up? Where's Kazu?
‐[Kenya] He went to go meet Aya.
‐How come?
‐You're joking, right?
It's not like she doesn't know
where our hideout is.
Maybe you should talk to him.
[Osamu] Oh, whatever.
Let's get going, already!
[others] OK.
[girls]
Goodbye, Mr. Yashiro.
‐[Osamu] Slow pokes
‐[Satoru] What's the rush?
[Hiromi] Wait up, guys!
[indistinct chatter]
[adult Satoru thinking]
Aya Nakanishi,
Hiromi Sugita,
and Kayo Hinazuki.
They're all still alive,
so I guess that means
the killer gave up on them.
But now that the clues
from the bus are gone,
how am I gonna find him?
There. Now he really
looks like a girl.
‐[laughter]
‐[Kazu] Whoa!
Now what? Are you done?
You know, playing detective.
Not yet.
I'm still on the case.
[adult Satoru narrating]
In 2006, my mom told Sawada
she thought she knew
who the killer was.
It's possible it's someone
she knows now, in 1988.
Maybe like Mr. Yashiro
and his candy,
the killer needs,
a substitute, too,
someone to take the place
of the kids that got away.
Move it.
Well, me and Kenya
are heading out now
to go watch the hockey game.
‐Is Hamada playing?
‐You know it.
Wish I could go.
When you see him,
tell him I said good luck.
‐Sure.
‐See ya later.
[Hiromi panting]
Here I am.
You notice how Misato's been
keeping to herself lately?
[Satoru] No. Really?
[Hiromi] Yeah.
People have been avoiding her,
ever since that lunch money
thing happened.
Oh, man. I guess I could try
talking to her on Monday.
[Hiromi] Cool.
[Satoru] Thanks for breakfast!
Oh, yeah,
I might be a little late today.
[Sachiko] Not too late, I hope.
When you know what time,
how about you call
and let me know, OK?
Mm‐hmm, I will.
See ya later, Mom!
Have a good day today, Satoru.
‐[girl 1] Mr. Yashiro's
gonna take us.
‐[girl 2] Really?
‐You‐know‐who will have to
walk over there.
‐[giggling]
‐[girl] Too bad for her.
‐[adult Satoru thinking]
What can I say to her?
Crap! Missed her.
Satoru, I heard you're gonna try
helping Misato next.
Mm‐hmm, but she just left.
I bet she's going
to Wakaba Gym.
‐Really?
‐Yeah, Hamada's playing,
so Mr. Yashiro invited her
to go cheer him on.
You know what, she went
to last week's game alone, too.
‐Thanks.
‐Want us to go with you?
Nah, I think I better
do this myself.
It's no biggie.
OK, but I want
a full report tomorrow.
Got it, Detective Satoru?
Sure.
We'll be at the hideout
if you need backup.
‐Mm‐hmm. See you later!
‐[Kazu] Later, dude!
‐[Osamu] See you tomorrow!
‐[Satoru] You got it.
‐[Kenya] Bye!
‐[Hiromi] See ya!
‐[Satoru] Bye, you guys!
Saying bye's
a big deal with him.
I know, right? He acts like
he'll never see us again.
Whoa! It's even colder
in here than outside.
[girl] Ohhh! Hamada!
Show 'em who's boss out there.
I can't concentrate
with you uglies yellin'!
‐Ah, we can yell if we want.
‐Watch the attitude, Kouichi.
‐Otherwise, no dinner for you.
‐What? But they're bugging me!
[girls laughing]
[chuckles]
[adult Satoru thinking]
There she is.
And she's alone.
‐All right, guys, warm up
and get your game face on.
‐[team] Yes, sir!
[adult Satoru thinking]
Now the killer's lost
two more potential victims,
it makes sense
he'd go for her next.
She's a perfect target.
She's going to the bathroom.
Game starts in five!
[player] You got it, coach!
[adult Satoru thinking]
Why is she taking so long?
[door opens]
[gulp]
I needed a candy break.
What's wrong?
The game's about to start.
Are you standing guard
for someone?
Huh? Oh, uh... no.
I just wanted to talk
to Misato.
Misato. Hmm...
Huh.
‐What, did she go outside?
‐Uh‐huh.
[adult Satoru thinking]
Where did she take off to?
That's Yuuki's dad's truck.
Mr. Yashiro,
I need to follow someone.
‐Will you drive?
‐[Yashiro] Hmm.
[Yashiro] That doesn't
even sound legal.
It's nothing bad.
We're just playing detective.
We pretend there's
a kidnapper at large.
Then we try to find girls
who seem like they're lonely
and make friends with them.
If anything, we could end up
stopping a real kidnapping.
My God, it might be just
a game, but it's a good idea.
I'm glad you think so.
Satoru, better buckle up.
Oh.
[Satoru straining]
[Yashiro] Oh, yeah.
I have to get that fixed.
There.
So, you've noticed Misato's been
keeping to herself lately.
[Satoru] Actually, Hiromi
told me a little while ago.
[Yashiro] Well, if you ask me,
it's great you're being
so proactive about it.
[Satoru] I don't know
about that.
I couldn't get up the nerve
to talk to her before,
and, well, I started thinking
she might make good bait.
Really? Bait.
So you're out to catch someone.
Now I know why you were working
so hard to be friendly
and outgoing.
You’re a man on a mission.
Mm‐hmm. Everybody has something
that's missing from their lives,
even me.
If I can fill that void...
[adult Satoru thinking] Crap.
I just fed him his own line.
[Yashiro] You and I
have a lot in common.
That happens to be
my philosophy in life.
When I teach
a sixth‐grade class,
I like to bring it up
in my graduation speech.
It sort of ties into
what you said,
about using Misato as bait?
I can tell you regret it,
but in my opinion,
you shouldn't.
There's no difference between
a good deed and a bad one.
They both have a similar goal,
to satisfy a need
within a person.
[adult Satoru thinking]
Well, that's... extreme.
[Yashiro] For example,
lately I've tried
all kinds of things
to get closer to someone.
Sometimes I'm direct,
other times I play coy.
At times,
I've even been deceitful.
And boy, it's been fun.
With who? A girlfriend?
[chuckles] I can see how you'd
make that connection.
Hmm. Either way, it's about
filling some kind of emptiness.
Um... want a lollipop?
Thank you for asking,
but I'm afraid you won't
find any there.
You see, this isn't my car.
Where is your car then?
In the shop?
[Yashiro] Whatever your happiest
moment is today,
another will eventually
come along to replace it.
And thanks to you,
mine just got replaced.
Nothing compares to the feeling
a person gets
when they can finally
satisfy their need.
You spent
all this time searching,
and when you get it,
it's like heaven.
You know,
it's true what they say,
the more effort something takes,
the sweeter the reward is.
[adult Satoru thinking]
Where the hell is he going
with this?
Laxatives?
[Yashiro] Satoru. You lied
to me a few minutes ago.
You said you're just pretending
there's a kidnapper,
but the truth is,
you know there's one,
and you're trying
to catch him.
I've resisted the idea
for a while now
because I couldn't believe
it was possible.
Well, more like
I didn't want to believe...
the possibility that someone
was anticipating my every move.
If you're still worried
about Misato, don't be.
The only person in that truck
is Jun Shiratori's father.
I realized something was up
with you
the day I saw you
following Aya Nakanishi.
And I was planning
to kidnap her
the day I gave
you and your mom a ride.
Looking back,
it's kind of funny.
I mean, there you were
trying to snatch my prey
and I was the one
telling you how to do it.
[chuckles]
That was the second time
you ruined my plans,
and I started to suspect
it was more than a coincidence.
I knew Misato's friends
were shunning her,
so I asked her
to the hockey game.
Then I told Hiromi about it.
If you showed up,
my suspicions were correct,
that you...
you were my enemy.
[adult Satoru thinking]
No way.
[Yashiro]
When the time was right,
I gave Misato a drink
laced with that laxative
you found.
And I bought dinner, to place
Shiratori at the scene.
[adult Satoru thinking]
No. No!
[Yashiro] Yes, sir,
all the pieces fit together
as planned.
And in the end,
I'm not who you thought I was.
Oh, and about the car,
I borrowed this one earlier.
I was looking for something
specific for today.
Generic model,
generic paint job.
A car that's so ubiquitous,
no one would even miss it.
You know, this is
the first time I've put
that theory into practice.
[adult Satoru thinking]
How could I be so stupid?!
It was so obvious.
Thanks to you, Kayo's alive.
[adult Satoru thinking]
I just couldn't accept
the possibility.
Yashiro was on one of Sawada's
lists of suspects.
But my mom's name
was right there with his,
so I figured the list was
bullshit and blew it off.
I trusted him so much,
I couldn't even think
of him as a suspect,
let alone the killer.
But...
he is.
And now he's got me
right where he wants me.
It started snowing.
[Satoru straining]
[Yashiro] Don't.
It's stuck for good.
[Satoru panting]
[Yashiro] The game's over.
For you and me.
[Satoru struggling]
You know,
I still can't believe it.
You anticipated all my plans
and destroyed them one by one.
I'm stunned how easily
you caught me,
a little boy like you.
It's almost like you can see
the future or something.
I want to make sure you
understand why you have to die.
Yes, you ruined my plans,
but this has nothing to do
with revenge.
Believe me, I do respect you.
But if I can't satisfy
my needs the usual way,
I have to find an alternative.
You don't have to do this.
You said the game was over!
The children of this town are
safe thanks to you, Satoru.
So congratulations,
you got what you wanted.
And as for what I wanted,
I still get to kill someone
for my sake and on my terms.
Yashiro, I'm not gonna die
until I see you hang
for what you've done!
Yes, well,
keep telling yourself that.
Yashiro!
You son of a bitch!
I'll get you for this!
I wish I could stay, but I have
so much packing to do.
Yashiro!
I know your future!
[adult Satoru thinking] Shit.
It's cold.
Come on, come on!
Going numb...
[young Satoru] Shit...
[Satoru] Mom?
[Sachiko] What's up, kiddo?
[adult Satoru narrating]
I looked up, our eyes met...
My friends...
[all] Hi, Satoru!
Thank you, Satoru.
Kayo.
Airi.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]