I have a name for
what happens to me: Revival.
[clang!]
When it happens,
I go back in time
anywhere from one
to five minutes.
Then it always happens
before something bad goes down.
I've managed to stop
a lot of tragedies, so far.
Hey there, Satoru.
Hey, Mom.
[screams]
[officer]
Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
You're gonna have to
come down to the station.
[theme song plays]
[man singing in Japanese]
See Mask Man?
Next week's the last episode!
Ah, I totally forgot
to watch Black!
[Satoru thinking] 1988.
February 15th?
[door opens]
‐Good morning, everyone.
‐[class] Good morning.
Well, Satoru,
you gonna take your seat?
[Satoru] Huh? Oh, yes, sir.
[adult Satoru thinking]
Where was my seat again?
You still asleep or something?
That's Kayo's desk,
you doofus.
[Satoru] Oh, yeah.
[teacher] No Kayo.
I'll have to mark her
tardy again.
[kids giggling]
Satoru, are you, like,
in love with Kayo?
[Satoru] Huh?
You'd make a cute couple.
You're both weird.
[teacher] Here we go, folks.
‐[adult Satoru thinking]
Is this for real?
‐[teacher calling roll]
Why did I get dropped
back to this time?
[various students]
Here! Here! Here!
‐Here! Here...
‐What's going on?
This is 18 years ago.
[watch ticking]
[bell chimes]
[boy] How far did you get
on Dragon Quest 3?
‐[boy 2] Level 15.
‐[boy 1] That's it?
‐[boy 2] Nah, just testing.
‐[boy 1] I'm on 25.
‐[boy 2] You liar!
[chair rattles]
Hey, what's wrong?
Um, my head hurts
so I'm gonna see the nurse.
Then why are you taking
your bag?
Don't worry about it.
I'll let the teacher know
where you went.
‐[Saturo panting]
‐[adult Satoru thinking]
What the hell's going on?
Is this Revival?
I don't get it.
Why'd I go back this far?
[gasp]
[groans]
Mom!
[doorbell rings]
[footsteps approaching]
[Satoru] H‐Hello.
[woman]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
[car door opens, closes]
[car drives off]
[adult Satoru thinking]
It's one of the neighbors.
That's right,
she'd be at work now.
Mom...
[door closes]
[footsteps]
Hey there, kiddo.
‐[Satoru] Mom!
‐What's wrong?
[Satoru] Nothing,
just happy to see you.
You little weirdo.
So what do you want for dinner?
Hamburger or meatballs?
Uh...
Hamburger?
You getting hungry or what?
Mm‐hmm.
[inhales, sighs]
[mother chuckles]
You're in a good mood,
not like this morning when
you pitched your little fit.
Guess you found
your recorder, huh?
Yeah, I did.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing to cry about,
kiddo.
[giggles]
[adult Satoru thinking]
I remember moments like this.
I guess back then
I didn't realize
how important they'd be.
I let times like this slip by
without even thinking
about them.
This is Revival.
It's another chance.
And there's no way
I'll let this one slip by.
‐Mom...
‐Hmm?
[Satoru] It's really good.
Thank you.
‐Are you sure you're OK?
‐[Satoru] Thanks for dinner.
[mother] You're welcome.
[adult Satoru thinking]
Am I supposed to do the next
18 years over again?
‐Good morning, Satoru!
‐Hey, Osamu. Morning.
If this is Revival,
then I'm here for one reason:
to stop something bad
from happening.
And maybe to save my mom,
I have to start here.
But why so far back?
Nothing seems off here.
Huh?
That's Kayo Hinazuki.
She lived alone
with her mom too.
[teacher] And bam.
[students] Wow!
How'd she get that?
[Osamu] You know what I think
sucks about this group?
There's no one
to talk Dragon Quest with.
[Satoru] Huh? Uh...
I mean, Hiro's
a Final Fantasy fan
and Kazu only plays shooters.
[adult Satoru thinking]
That's Hiro and Kazu.
I remember them.
Heck, Satoru doesn't even
have a Famicom.
No, I didn't.
Jeez, Osamu, if we all played
Dragon Quest,
then that's all we'd ever
talk about.
The cool thing
about our group is,
we all like different things
so it's never boring.
That's Kenya.
Out of all of us,
he was the brainiest.
Can I ask you something, Satoru?
It's kind of personal.
Sure. Go ahead.
[Kenya] Do you have
a crush on Kayo?
[gasp]
I saw you staring at her.
‐No way. Really?
‐He totally was.
This morning
he just stood there staring.
‐He couldn't take
his eyes off her.
‐Dang it, Satoru.
If you're in love with her,
you should have come
to me for advice.
‐Romance is right up my alley.
‐But...
No "buts" about it.
I'll fix it so's you
can hook up with Kayo.
Could you keep your voice down?
[Kazu] Why?
Well, it's like...
I don't love her.
Just curious about her.
‐That's the same thing.
‐You're brave to admit it.
Don't you worry about a thing.
By the end of today, you'll be
talking with your dream girl.
‐You're an idiot.
‐Damn, she's cold.
‐That's how you say hello?
I said that out loud.
Ah, crap.
I bet Kazu straight up told her
I have a crush on her.
Um... Kayo?
I was thinking,
since we walk home the same way,
maybe we could be friends?
Friends?
What is it you like about me?
[adult Satoru thinking]
Oh, she's a pain in the ass.
[Kayo] You don't have to answer
that if you don't want to.
I think I know.
You're just like I am.
You're fake, too.
Wait...
does she know about me?
[Kayo] I saw you
running home yesterday.
You looked happy.
Do you love your mom that much?
Yeah.
That's good.
[Satoru] Wait, Kayo, hold up!
So how about it?
You wanna be friends?
[Kayo] Are you serious?
So, like, does that mean
you'd kill to protect me?
[young Satoru]
No, you don't get it,
I could have saved her!
[adult Satoru thinking]
Something bad was happening
to Kayo
in the days before she died.
Maybe if I can stop it,
I can save her.
[Kayo] I think I know.
You're just like I am.
You're fake, too.
[adult Satoru thinking]
I doubt she could tell
I wasn't really a kid.
‐[boy 1] It's so yellow.
‐[boy 2] Quit it!
I guess maybe I might have
been acting a little weird,
but that's pretty much
how I was back in those days.
I wanted friends,
so I tried acting like
the person I wanted to be.
If you have courage,
you can do anything.
It was the only way
I knew how to fit in
in my middle school world.
[Osamu] We were gonna
send a search party in...
I bet she saw through that,
but she said I was like her,
so maybe she's hiding
her true self too.
So, how'd you make out?
Yeah, man, you gonna tell us
how it went or what?
Did you guys walk home together,
did you hold hands?
Jeez, no. We just talked
for a little bit, that's all.
‐[Osamu] Just you two, alone?
‐Mm‐hmm.
Sweet! That means
she totally likes you.
Dude, seriously, she never
talks to anyone alone.
‐You want me to give her
another message? Do ya?
‐[Satoru sighs]
[adult Satoru thinking]
Could they be more annoying?
Take it easy, guys.
‐Pressuring him like this
isn't gonna help him.
‐[Kazu] You're right.
[adult Satoru thinking]
He's talking about
something else, but, yeah.
Satoru, in sixth grade, we'll
all be in the same class again,
so there's no rush.
Right.
[woman over loudspeaker]
Attention, students...
[adult Satoru thinking]
When did Kayo disappear, again?
I'm running out of time!
‐[Osamu] Hey, Satoru, come on.
‐[Satoru] Yeah, coming.
[Osamu] Brrr!
It's cold. By the way,
where are those kick‐ass
McGregor gloves you got?
Oh yeah. I remember I had
a pair of those.
[Satoru] I guess maybe
I left them somewhere.
[Osamu] Oh. Well, they're
probably at the hideout then.
Hey, guys, can we
go to the hideout today?
What are you talking about?
Remember? We said we wouldn't
go there if it snows,
'cause everyone would see
our tracks.
Oh, w‐we did?
Oh, right, yeah. [awkward laugh]
‐[Osamu] See you tomorrow.
‐[Kazu] Later, dudes.
‐[Kenya] Later.
‐[Hiromi] Bye.
‐[Satoru] See ya.
Kenya! Thanks for speaking up.
It's like, they were making
such a big deal out of it,
I was freaking out.
Yeah, I bet you were.
You don't have
to thank me, though.
By the way, about Kayo...
I think it's great you want
to get closer to her and all,
but I get the feeling
there's something else going on.
‐[Satoru gasps]
‐[Kenya] I don't mean
to be nosy or anything, but...
I'm here if you need
to talk to someone.
And not just me.
The other guys are, too.
[Satoru] Thanks. And yeah...
I know everyone's
just trying to help.
Kazu did get Kayo
to talk to me after all.
So, wanna talk about it?
‐About what?
‐About Kayo.
‐Oh, right.
‐Did you talk to her?
Yeah. Only for a bit.
‐She even opened up
a little by the end.
‐That's good.
[Kenya] I know you've got
a lot on your mind,
but I was wondering...
[car revving past]
‐You read the essays yet?
‐Huh?
No, I haven't.
There are a couple
of interesting ones.
You should check them out.
I better go.
See you tomorrow.
[Satoru] See ya.
[adult Satoru thinking]
I think Kenya was hinting
at Kayo's essay being
the interesting one in this.
[Kayo] "A Town Without Me,"
by Kayo Hinazuki.
"When I get bigger, big enough
to go somewhere by myself,
I want to go someplace
far away from here.
I want to go to an island,
an island without any people,
an island that doesn't have any
pain or sadness on it either.
There are no grown‐ups, kids,
classmates or teachers.
Even my mom's not there.
When I feel like
I wanna climb a tree,
I can climb it.
I'll go for a swim
if I want to.
And sleep when I want to.
On the island,
I'll think about what's going
on in the town without me.
Kids go to school
like nothing's changed,
grown‐ups go to work like
nothing's changed.
Mom eats her dinner
like nothing's changed.
And when I think about
the town without me,
I feel relief
more than anything.
All I want is to go far away."
[adult Satoru thinking]
Her essay's a cry for help.
‐No doubt about it.
‐[door opens]
[mother] I'm home.
‐Thanks for dinner.
‐Hmm?
Kenya probably thought
I was interested in her
'cause of the essay.
After reading it, now I'm
even more worried about her.
‐Hey, Mom?
‐Yeah, what's up?
For my birthday,
can I invite some friends over?
Mm‐hmm, sure, but our place
is kind of small.
How many friends
are we talkin'?
Not too many, just five.
You know, this is the first time
you asked to have a party.
Should I get a big cake?
Yeah! Thanks, Mom.
I know what I have to do now.
I have to get to know Kayo
even better.
I'm gonna do what I didn't
the first time.
If I can make her
do something different now,
maybe it will be enough
to change her fate.
Maybe it'll change everything.
[mother] Hey, you still awake?
You said five.
Did you get yourself
a girlfriend?
All right, good night, kiddo.
[adult Satoru thinking] Witch.
I just remembered something.
I didn't show my mom
my essay back then
because I knew she'd read it
and see right into my soul.
What did I write about again?
[bell chiming]
[boy 1] I'm going home
and play Dragon Quest.
[boy 2] Me too!
[Kazu] Man, it's snowing again.
No hideout today.
Satoru! Kayo's leaving.
Don't you want to talk to her?
[Kenya] Osamu...
It's OK, Kenya.
It's no big deal.
And thanks, Osamu.
See ya!
‐See you.
‐Later, dude.
‐Whoa!
‐Can you believe
how brave he's gotten?
[adult Satoru thinking]
I didn't have to run.
I already knew
where I'd find Kayo.
I was pretty sure
her mom was hitting her,
and if that was true,
she wouldn't be going home
right away.
She'd go hang out at the park
until it got darker out.
Before I just thought
she was weird.
Not anymore.
[Satoru] Kayo!
[Kayo] Satoru. What do you think
you're doing out here?
[Satoru] I was gonna say
the same thing.
I meant what I said,
I wanna be friends.
I won't kill anyone,
that's too much.
[Kayo] No duh. That was a joke.
[adult Satoru sighs]
I hate dealing with her type.
[Kayo] I know what you're
doing, Satoru.
You're just pretending.
Pretending to smile
and being nice
and worrying about people.
But I don't think
it's bad or anything.
I can't tell what you're
really like.
That sounds funny
coming from me.
[sighs]
Everything you said's true.
I am pretending.
I want people to like me.
I wanna have friends.
So I asked myself,
what can a loser like me
do to have that?
And you know what?
I tried liking everyone
and it worked.
It was hard at first,
but after a while,
it got easier.
Yeah.
And, like, the more you do it,
the better the chance
it comes true.
The more I talk about it,
the better the chance
it will come true.
[adult Satoru thinking]
It's like
déjà vu all over again.
To get what you want,
you have to make an effort.
You have to try new things
and keep inspiring yourself.
That's how you change.
Is that what Kayo's doing, too?
I can tell she's suffering now.
But unlike me,
she acts like she doesn't care.
Pretending like she can't
feel anything at all.
But she's only 10.
She's not strong enough
to change her situation
at home.
[Satoru] Hey, Kayo,
I brought something for you.
[Kayo] What?
[Satoru] I'm having
a birthday party
and I want you to come.
Uh... are you sure it's OK?
I mean, won't there be
tons of people?
[Satoru] Oh, I don't know yet.
But I wanted to give you
the first invitation.
It's on March the 2nd.
You're gonna come, right?
Uh‐huh.
Hey, aren't your hands cold?
[Satoru] Huh? Oh, yeah.
They kind of are.
I had some new gloves,
but I think I lost them.
[adult Satoru thinking]
Take it easy, dude. You're 29.
Why are you getting
all flustered?
Satoru, are you OK?
Uh... uh‐huh.
I mean, my hand's way bigger
than yours, huh?
You're an idiot.
Even so...
you seem like you're OK.
It's easy talking to you.
Well...
‐It's 'cause I decided
‐to be honest with you.
I said that out loud.
Wait, Kayo!
So, um, see ya tomorrow?
[adult Satoru thinking]
She didn't have gloves
either, did she?
Eighteen years ago,
I saw Kayo here, alone.
And then she disappeared.
If I remember right,
they found her body
after the snow melted.
[young Satoru] This time,
I won't leave her
standing here all alone.
This time...
[adult Satoru thinking]
I'm going to save her.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]