[LOREILE] PRINCESS NUREHA!
PRINCESS NUREHA!
(VOICE CHAT PING) IT'S ME,
LONDARK... HAS SHE RETURNED?
[LONDARK] NO, NOT YET. YOU ARE
AWARE HOW IMPULSIVE SHE CAN BE.
[LOREILE] IS MIZPHA EVEN GOING
TO TRY LOOKING FOR HER?
[LONDARK] OH YES, GENERAL MIZPHA
HAS A MESSAGE FOR YOU.
SAYS THEY ARE CURRENTLY
IN THE PROCESS
OF CARRYING OUT
OPERATION: RED NIGHT.
[LONDARK] FURTHERMORE,
IF PRINCESS NUREHA WANTS
TO GO OFF ON ONE OF
HER EXCURSIONS...
IT IS NOT OUR PLACE
TO QUESTION HER.
[LOREILE] WAS THAT SUPPOSED TO
BE SARCASM, LONDARK?
HER MAJESTY PRESIDES
OVER PLANT HWAYDEN
AS OUR COMMANDER IN CHIEF!
(GRUNT)
[LOREILE] PRINCESS NUREHA... YOU
SHOULD'VE LET ME COME WITH YOU
AS IS MY DUTY AS YOUR ESCORT IF
YOU WANTED TO FIND
YOUR WAY BACK HOME!
[LOREILE, THINKING]
WEST IT IS!
(LAUGHTER)
[MINORI] UH? IT'S THEM AGAIN.
[ALL] HM?
[RUDY] YEAH. WONDER
WHAT THEY'RE UP TO...
[DARIELLA] AROUND HERE,
IT'S NOT ALL THAT UNUSUAL
TO SEE THE ODYSSEY KNIGHTS.
[SERARA] THAT'S KINDA STRANGE.
PEOPLE OF THE LAND THINK OF
THEM AS A GROUP OF HEROES.
[DARIELLA] WHEN YOU CONSIDER ALL
THE TIME THEY SPEND RISKING
THEIR LIFE TO SAVE
TOWNS AND VILLAGES.
[SERARA] MAYBE. BUT THEY
LOOK A LITTLE SCARY,
LIKE THEY'RE LOOKING
FOR A FIGHT.
BUT THEY'RE ALSO KINDA
COOL, YOU KNOW?
[ISUZU] HUH? YOU THINK SO?
I GUESS THEY LOOK LIKE
DEPENDABLE FIGHTERS, ANYWAY.
[TOYA] I DON'T LIKE IT...
SOMETHING ABOUT THEM
RUBS ME THE WRONG WAY.
[MINORI] I FEEL THE SAME,
AND I'M NOT SURE WHY...
[ALL] THANK YOU FOR THE FOOD!
AH!(MUNCH)
[SERARA] HOW'S THE FOOD
THIS TIME, YOU GUYS?
I REALLY DIDN'T CHANGE
ANYTHING ALL THAT MUCH...
[ISUZU] MAYBE, BUT IT TURNED
OUT FANTASTIC THIS TIME!
[TOYA] YEAH, I REALLY LIKE THIS.
[MINORI] YOU KEEP GETTING
BETTER AND BETTER AT IT!
[RUDY] AND JUST LOOK
AT THE CLEAR NIGHT SKY!
THIS REALLY IS A
DELIGHTFUL DINNER!
[DARIELLA] ALL OF YOU CERTAINLY
ARE CLOSE, AREN'T YOU?
[MINORI] WE'RE ALL FRIENDS HERE!
GOOD FRIENDS, REALLY.
[DARIELLA] IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT IS IT THAT LEADS YOU
TO THE REDSTONE MOUNTAINS?
[TOYA] WE'RE HUNTING WYVERNS!
MAGIC BAGS ARE MADE
OF THEIR HIDES.
[DARIELLA]
OH REALLY, HOW EXCITING.
[ISUZU] AFTER ALL THE MILES
WE'VE BEEN PUTTING IN,
SHOULDN'T WE BE PRETTY
CLOSE TO SAPHIR VILLAGE?
[DARIELLA]
YOU'RE NOT TOO FAR NOW.
[ISUZU] OH, YEAH? HAVE
YOU BEEN THERE BEFORE?
IT'S ON MY WAY BACK HOME...
SO I'VE GONE THROUGH IT.
I'D LOVE TO PUT ON A
CONCERT WHEN WE GET THERE!
[DARIELLA] A CONCERT, YOU SAY?
[ROE2] WHAT'S A "CONCERT"?
I DON'T THINK MISS ROE2 HAS
HEARD YOU PLAY YOUR LUTE YET.
[MINORI] ISUZU'S A BARD OR WHAT
YOU'D CALL A WANDERING MINSTREL.
[ISUZU] EHEHEHEH! I'M NOT
REALLY ALL THAT GOOD YET.
[MINORI] WHEREVER WE
STOP ALONG THE WAY,
SHE PUTS ON A SHOW AND
SINGS A FEW SONGS.
OH! SO YOU'RE A MUSICIAN?
[ISUZU]
EHEHEHE!
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, PEOPLE
ACTUALLY STARTED CALLING ME
"ROCK STAR" BACK AT THE
AKIHABARA BROOMHALL!
[ROE2] AND WHAT'S A "ROCK STAR"?
[SERARA] WELL IT'S LIKE...
SHE'S A POP IDOL...
AND THAT SHE'S REALLY COOL!
THAT'S KINDA VAGUE!
DEFINITELY VAGUE!
[ROE2] WELL I'D LOVE TO HEAR
YOU PLAY US A SONG,
IF THAT'D BE ALRIGHT.
[DARIELLA]
YES, THAT WOULD BE LOVELY!
[BOTH]
EHEH!
[TOYA]
OH!
OKAY, THAT'S IT!
SAPHIR VILLAGE IS
GETTING A CONCERT!
(CHEERING)
(ISUZU SINGING, MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHOOPS, HOLLERS, CHEERS)
HEY! THANKS, EVERYONE!
YOU WANNA HEAR ONE MORE?
[ISUZU]
ALL RIGHT THEN! YOU GOT IT!
(SURGE OF CHEERS)
[ISUZU] AHHH... THAT WAS GREAT,
BUT I COULD NOT
EAT ANOTHER BITE!
[RUDY] MISS ISUZU, MAYBE
IT WOULDN'T HURT YOU
TO SAY 'NO' EVERY
ONCE IN A WHILE!
[ISUZU] YEAH, BUT IT WOULD'VE
BEEN RUDE! BUT YOU'RE SWEET.
[ISUZU] SERIOUSLY! I'D
NEVER BEEN ANYWHERE WHERE
PEOPLE JUST KEPT ON
BUYING ME FOOD LIKE THAT!
[RUDY] I MUST SAY THE CONCERT
TONIGHT WAS TRULY AMAZING.
THERE YOU GO AGAIN...
EXAGGERATING.
HMPH! DON'T EVEN...
YOU'RE GREAT!
(ISUZU HUMMING "YOUR SONG")
[RUDY] HM? YOUR
OVERWHELMING LOVE OF MUSIC
KNOWS NO BOUNDS DOES IT?
[ISUZU] I GUESS IT DOESN'T.
[RUDY] SO WHY DO YOU
KEEP SECOND GUESSING
THE WAY YOU PERFORM?
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
HUH? WELL... IT'S
NOT LIKE I'M TRYING
TO BE HUMBLE OR
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
[RUDY]
HUH?
[ISUZU] I DON'T KNOW IF
I SAID THIS BEFORE...
BUT BACK WHERE I COME FROM,
MY DAD IS ACTUALLY A
PROFESSIONAL MUSICIAN.
AH WELL THEN, I GUESS IT MAKES
SENSE THAT YOU WOULD HAVE
AN INHERENT LOVE AND PENCHANT
FOR ALL THINGS MUSIC.
COME ON! DON'T BLOW IT
OUT OF PROPORTION.
ITS JUST THAT MY DAD...
HE'S REALLY GOOD, THE EPITOME OF
A ROCKER! HE'S TOTALLY COOL...
HIS HAIR IS LONG, AND HE'S
ALWAYS GOT
HIS LEATHER JACKET ON!
AND I SWEAR, HE'S SO SKINNY!
AND HE'D LOVE TO TELL STORIES
ABOUT WHAT HE DID ON THE ROAD!
SOUNDED LIKE A BLAST.
IT WAS ALL ABOUT THE MUSIC,
HE DIDN'T HAVE ANY MONEY.
HE'D JUST CRAM ALL
HIS INSTRUMENTS
IN AN OLD BEAT‐UP
MINIVAN AND HIT THE ROAD!
FIRST STOP, TOKYO...
LAST STOP ANYWHERE
AND HIT EVERYWHERE IN BETWEEN!
[RUDY] KINDA SOUNDS
LIKE US, DOESN'T IT?
[ISUZU] YEAH, EXACTLY!
[RUDY] HEH...! IT SOUNDS
LIKE HE'S A WONDERFUL FATHER.
[ISUZU] I KNOW, RIGHT?!
HE CAN BE KINDA NUTTY...
BUT MY DAD HAS ALWAYS
BEEN A HERO TO ME.
HE AND HIS BAND EVEN
MANAGED TO GET A CONTRACT!
HUH? WHAT'S A CONTRACT FOR?
[ISUZU] WELL, IT'S WHEN A RECORD
LABEL PICKS YOU UP, AND...
[RUDY] HUH?
UH... WELL, I...
WHAT I MEAN IS...
IS HE GOT FAMOUS!
THEY PROMOTED HIS BAND...
AND THEN YOU COULD
HEAR HIS MUSIC
PLAYING EVERYWHERE!
NOW, THAT'S REALLY SOMETHING!
THE THING IS... BACK IN
THE WORLD I COME FROM...
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE
WHO CAN PLAY LIKE MY DAD.
RECORD COMPANIES GIVE ABOUT
A HUNDRED BANDS IN JAPAN,
THE CHANCE TO MAKE
A DEBUT LIKE THAT,
BUT THEY DON'T LAST.
[RUDY] UH...
OUT OF THAT HUNDRED,
ONLY A HANDFUL
MAKE IT AFTER
THEY GET PUSHED.
MY DAD DIDN'T MAKE IT.
HE WAS GOOD, BUT PEOPLE
DIDN'T BUY HIS ALBUMS.
DID HE DECIDE TO GIVE
UP ON MUSIC THEN?
NO WAY... HE LOVED
MUSIC TOO MUCH
TO JUST GIVE UP
ON IT LIKE THAT.
SO HE PICKED HIMSELF BACK UP AND
KEPT ON WORKING AS A SESSION
PLAYER. [RUDY] UHH...
[ISUZU] OH... KAY... THAT'S
A LITTLE TOUGHER TO EXPLAIN.
OK! HOW ABOUT THIS!
HE'S A PRO'S‐PRO!
HE PLAYS SESSIONS IN STUDIO,
BUT WITH OTHER PEOPLE'S BANDS.
OKAY, SO TELL ME MISS ISUZU...
ISN'T THIS YOUR DEBUT?
[ISUZU] OF COURSE NOT!
RECORD COMPANIES DECIDE THAT!
BUT EVERYONE'S BEEN
ENJOYING WHAT YOU'RE DOING!
THAT'S A PRO TO ME!
YEAH, WELL IT TAKES MORE
THAN THAT. [RUDY] HUH?
[ISUZU] I'M..., I'M SORRY.
I JUST KNOW A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT HOW THAT WORLD WORKS.
DON'T GET ME WRONG! I DO
LOVE PLAYING THE LUTE!
DEFINITELY...!
AND SINGING, TOO...
IT'S JUST THAT I, UH..
I DON'T... REALLY HAVE
THE TALENT. [RUDY] UH...
[ISUZU] MY DAD ALWAYS TOLD ME,
YOU GOTTA KEEP KICKING YOURSELF
EVERYDAY TO MAKE IT
IN THIS BUSINESS.
THAT A LOT OF
MUSICIANS ARE TALENTED.
AND THAT YOU NEED TO PUT IN THE
HOURS, UNTIL YOUR FINGERS BLEED,
AND STILL THAT WON'T BE ENOUGH
FOR SOME PEOPLE! [RUDY] I SEE...
[ISUZU] JUST UNDERSTAND...
I'M DOING THIS FOR FUN, OKAY?
[ISUZU] AND I'M GLAD EVERYONE
LIKES THE SHOWS WE'RE DOING!
[RUDY] NOT JUST THEM, I LOVE
YOUR SONGS, TOO, ISUZU.
[ISUZU] HUH... THAT'S
REALLY NICE OF YOU...
BUT I'M NEVER GONNA END UP
PLAYING AS WELL AS MY FATHER.
YOU'RE TOO HARD ON YOURSELF...
JUST WATCH THE CROWD...
THEY ABSOLUTELY ADORE YOU
WHEN YOU GET UP AND PLAY.
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE
THEIR 42 GODDESS.
HUH? WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
RUDY, SOMETIMES I
DON'T THINK WE'RE EVEN
TALKING ABOUT THE SAME THING.
[RUDY] OH UH...?
YOU DON'T KNOW 42?
[ISUZU] UH...?
[SERARA] YEAH... TOTALLY...
[MINORI] IT HAPPENED TO YOU TOO?
[SERARA] I WENT TO THE
STORE THE OTHER DAY
TO GET SOME BOILED
FISH PASTE AND
THEY WOUND UP GIVING
ME BOILED FLOUR PASTE.
IT'S CRAZY RIGHT. THE APP
MUST BE MESSED UP OR SOMETHING.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THE AUTOMATIC TRANSLATE APP.
I LOVE THAT THING! HOW
ELSE WOULD WE TALK TO
ALL THE PEOPLE
FROM OTHER COUNTRIES.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT. THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND HAVE
A SEPARATE LANGUAGE
ALL THEIR OWN.
WE'VE BEEN USING IT TO TALK TO
THEM SINCE THE BEGINNING...
IT'S BEEN GREAT... IN FACT, I
ALMOST FORGET IT WAS EVEN THERE,
'CAUSE IT'S ONLY NOW THAT
IT'S BEEN ACTING WEIRD.
[SERARA] OKAY THEN,
WHAT'S CHANGED?
I DON'T KNOW, IT COULD
BE ANYTHING, I GUESS...
I JUST KNOW THIS
SORT OF THING IS
HAPPENING MORE
AND MORE LATELY.
[SERARA] THAT COULD BE IT.
MIGHT EXPLAIN WHY
WE DON'T UNDERSTAND
EACH OTHER THESE DAYS?
FOR EXAMPLE, SEVEN
COLORS UP IN THE SKY?
RAINBOW?
[RUDY] EXACTLY,
BUT THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
DON'T SAY RAINBOW.
THEY SAY "SEVEN
COLORS IN THE SKY."
SO WHAT DOES "42" MEAN?
IT MEANS, "MUSIC."
HUH? WHY'S THAT?
BECAUSE TO THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND...
THERE ARE ONLY
42 COMPOSITIONS.
[ISUZU] HUH?
OUR ANCIENT ANCESTORS
HAD 42 SONGS
BESTOWED UPON THEM BY
THE GODS OF THIS WORLD.
... AND WE SIMPLY DON'T HAVE THE
ABILITY TO MAKE OUR OWN MUSIC.
WAIT A MINUTE... IS THAT
LEFTOVER PART OF THE GAME?
[RUDY] IT'S JUST THE ONLY MUSIC
WE WERE GIVEN, AND NO MORE.
IT'S BEEN THAT WAY ALL MY LIFE.
I JUST THOUGHT THE WHOLE
THING WAS NATURAL,
AND NEVER REALLY QUESTIONED IT.
[ISUZU, THINKING] NO WAY...
IS HE REALLY SERIOUS
ABOUT THIS?!
[RUDY] AND THAT IS WHY... WE
ALL LOVE IT WHEN YOU PLAY...
WE CAN'T HELP OURSELVES
BECAUSE IT'S ALL NEW TO US.
(GASP)
YOU JUST HAVE TO LOOK
OUT IN THE CROWD,
AND YOU'LL SEE IT IN THEIR EYES.
I'VE SEEN SOME OF 'EM CRYING
WHEN THEY HEARD YOUR SONGS.
THEY WERE OVERCOME WITH JOY
WITH EVERY SINGLE NOTE.
AND THEY'VE NEVER
EXPERIENCED THAT BEFORE.
THEY JUST WANTED TO GET UP AND
DANCE
OR JUST HOLD ONTO
THEIR LOVED ONES
AND JUST DRINK THEMSELVES SILLY
WITH THE FEELING YOU GAVE THEM!
SERIOUSLY. WE'VE NEVER HEARD
ANYTHING LIKE WHAT YOU DO.
AND FOR SHARING THEM WITH US,
YOU'RE LIKE OUR OWN HERO,
MISS ISUZU. I MEAN IT.
YOU'RE SOMETHING SPECIAL.
[ISUZU]
AH...?
[ISUZU] OH RUDY...
SO DO YOU THINK ISUZU'S GONNA
BE A PROFESSIONAL MUSICIAN?
[MINORI] I DON'T KNOW, BUT SHE
SEEMS TO LIKE IT. IT'S AWESOME.
SHE'S GOT A TALENT.
SOMETHING SHE'S GOOD AT.
IT MUST BE GREAT TO HAVE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I TOTALLY GET WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING ABOUT HER ABILITIES!
IN FACT, I'M KINDA JEALOUS OF
HOW SHE CAN SING AND PLAY
THE LUTE LIKE THAT!
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
[MINORI] SO, DO YOU
HAVE SOMETHING THAT
YOU'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO LEARN HOW TO DO?
[SERARA] YOU MEAN
LIKE IF WE EVER END UP
GOING BACK TO
THE REAL WORLD?
[MINORI] WELL NOT JUST THAT...
EVEN IF WE CAN'T GET BACK...
WHAT DO YOU REALLY WANNA DO?
[SERARA] NOW THAT'S KINDA
TOUGH. I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST ENJOYING MY LIFE.
[MINORI] 'KAY THEN.
[SERARA] BUT I BET YOU'VE PUT
SOME GOOD THOUGHT INTO IT.
[MINORI] YEAH, WELL...
I SURE HAVE...
I HAVE A DREAM I'M SHOOTING FOR.
[MINORI, THINKING] I WANT TO
BE JUST LIKE MASTER SHIROE,
BUT WHAT DOES THAT MEAN EXACTLY?
HE IS WHO HE IS. WE DON'T
NEED ANOTHER SHIROE.
AND LET'S FACE IT, NO ONE CAN
DO WHAT HE DOES AS WELL AS HIM.
[MINORI] OH JUST FORGET IT!
I'M MAKING MY BRAIN HURT!
[SERARA] DO YOU
NEED AN ASPIRIN?!
[RUDY] HERE'S SOMETHING
ELSE TO THINK ABOUT:
DID YOU NOTICE ALL THE
YOUNG PEOPLE OF THE LAND
COMING TO THE CITY?
[ISUZU] NUH‐UH.
[RUDY] EVERY ONE OF THEM
WAS COMING TO AKIHABARA
WITH A DREAM.
THERE ARE BLACKSMITHS AND
TAILORS AND CHEFS
AND WARRIORS AMONG
THEM... EVEN MUSICIANS.
EVEN IF THEY JUST SPEND A FEW
MONTHS IN AKIHABARA
THEY'LL BE ABLE
TO PICK UP SKILLS
THAT THEY PROBABLY WON'T BE
ABLE TO LEARN ANYWHERE ELSE.
THEY CAN BECOME
ANYTHING, MISS ISUZU!
YOU MEAN LIKE YOU DID?
YEAH, LIKE ME, AND JUST
LOOK WHERE I AM NOW.
I'M AN ADVENTURER, MISS ISUZU.
OF COURSE, I DIDN'T DO IT
ON MY OWN, I HAD SOME SUPPORT
FROM MY FRIENDS BACK HOME.
[ISUZU] UH...
[RUDY]
I STILL GO SEE THEM SOMETIMES.
IT'S WHY I DISAPPEAR
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
AKIHABARA ISN'T AN
EASY PLACE TO LIVE...
'SPECIALLY IF YOU'RE ONE OF US.
SO WE TRY TO HELP
EACH OTHER OUT.
BUT JUST LOOK AT
ALL THE COOL STUFF
THAT GOES ON THERE EVERY DAY!
PARADES, FESTIVALS, FOOD, MAGES
DOING TRICKS FOR ENTERTAINMENT?!
I MEAN, THIS PLACE IS GREAT!
IT'S LIKE THE IMPOSSIBLE
IS NOW POSSIBLE.
SO THIS MUSIC YOU'VE
STARTED PLAYING...?
IT'S A RADIANT MIRACLE.
[ISUZU]
YOU'VE ALL BEEN PLANNING THINGS
ABOUT HOW YOU WANT YOUR LIVES
TO BE, AND WHO YOU WANT TO BE.
AND THEN, I WALK INTO
YOUR LIVES... [RUDY] HMM?
I START SINGING ABOUT
LIFE AND LOVE AND
ALL THE THINGS I
WANNA DO FOR ME...
IT'S SO EMBARRASSING!
[RUDY] I DIDN'T MEAN TO MAKE
YOU CRY...! WHAT I MEANT...
[ISUZU]
PLEASE... DON'T...
[RUDY]
HMM...
COULD YOU... GIMME
A LITTLE SPACE?
[RUDY]
AS YOU WISH.
(SOBS)
(ISUZU CRYING)
OH, GOD...
(INHALE, SNIFF)
I DIDN'T... I DIDN'T KNOW...
(YAWNS)
[TOYA] CHOSHI WAS ON A
RIVER, TOO, WASN'T IT?
AT FIRST, I DIDN'T GET IT...
BUILDING BY THE RIVER...
THEN I REMEMBERED THAT
BEING NEAR THE WATER HELPS
WITH FARMING AND DAILY LIFE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WAIT
FOR RAIN OR ANYTHING.
THAT AND IT LOOK LIKE THERE'S A
BUNCH OF PLANT LIFE AROUND HERE.
I GUESS THAT STUFF
YOU LEARN IN SCHOOL
CAN COME IN HANDY AFTER ALL...
UH...?
(EXHALE)
(STARTLED)
[DARIELLA]
UH...!
WELL HELLO THERE, GOOD
MORNING TO YOU, TOYA.
[TOYA]
UH, MORNING!
[DARIELLA] WHY DON'T YOU
COME AND JOIN ME DOWN HERE?
[TOYA]
UH, SURE.
MISS DARIELLA, HAVE YOU
BEEN OUT HERE ALL MORNING?
[DARIELLA] YES, I USUALLY
DON'T NEED THAT MUCH SLEEP.
[TOYA] YOU SAID YOU WERE
FROM MINAMI, RIGHT?
[DARIELLA] YES, BUT I'M
USUALLY ON THE ROAD.
AS A CHRONICLER, I SEEK OUT
LITTLE ADVENTURES
AND WRITE DOWN WHAT
I SEE ALONG THE WAY.
HOWEVER, WHEN I'M NOT OUT
ON THE ROAD,
I HAVE A LITTLE COTTAGE
IN IKOMA. [TOYA] IKOMA?
[DARIELLA] IT'S VERY SECLUDED,
TUCKED AWAY
JUST OUTSIDE OF KYOTO.
[TOYA] OKAY.
[DARIELLA] BUT
HONESTLY, THINGS CAN GET
SOMEWHAT LONELY ON
THE MOUNTAINSIDE.
PEOPLE AREN'T EXACTLY CLAMBERING
UP THERE TO KEEP ME COMPANY.
SO ON OCCASION, I GET THE URGE
TO GET OUT AND VISIT THE CITY.
[TOYA]
ISN'T THAT DANGEROUS?
[DARIELLA]
I'M USED TO IT BY NOW.
MONSTERS AREN'T MUCH OF A
PROBLEM ANYMORE EVER SINCE
PLANT HWAYDEN TOOK OVER THE
DUTIES
OF PROVIDING SECURITY
FOR THE AREA.
SOMETHING ABOUT THAT
NAME SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
(BREATH, EXHALE)
THEIR ACHIEVEMENTS IN
ADMINISTERING THINGS IN MINAMI
HAVE LEFT THE CITY
WEALTHY AND BEAUTIFUL!
BUT IT SOUNDS AS IF
YOU DON'T CARE FOR IT.
I DON'T KNOW ALL
THAT MUCH ABOUT IT.
WELL IF YOU EVER GET THE
CHANCE TO SEE MINAMI MAYBE
YOU CAN COME VISIT
ME AT MY HOUSE.
UH...!
AND IF YOU HAVE THE TIME,
WE CAN GO SEE THE CITY TOGETHER.
WOULDN'T YOU LIKE THAT, TOYA?
(ANNOYED)
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG TOYA,
WHY WON'T YOU LOOK AT ME?
I'M FINE, OKAY?
YOU CAN TRY AND DENY
IT IF YOU WANT...
YOU DON'T HATE ME DO YOU?
I'M JUST NOT SURE ABOUT YOU.
(GIGGLE)
CAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS SMILING.
[DARIELLA]
YES. I SUPPOSE SO.
WHAT ABOUT IT?
[TOYA] YOU DON'T HAVE
TO FAKE IT, YOU KNOW?
[DARIELLA]
UH...?
THERE YOU GO, I LIKE THAT.
ALRIGHT THEN,
IF YOU THINK SO...
WHY WOULD YOU SAY SOMETHING
LIKE THAT TO ME?
[SHIROE]
AHHH!
[AKATSUKI]
UH... RUDE.
YOU JUST SURPRISED
ME THAT'S ALL,
HOW'D YOU GET IN HERE ANYWAY?
[AKATSUKI]
THROUGH THE WINDOW.
OKAY, BUT YOU'RE WELCOME
TO USE THE DOOR. SO?
I'VE COMPLETED MY RECONNAISSANCE
MISSION WITHOUT INCIDENT.
AND I GATHERED ALL THE
INTELLIGENCE I COULD FIND.
[SHIROE] IT'S NOT
LIKE I SENT YOU ON
A SUPER‐SECRET SPY MISSION.
MAY I GIVE YOU MY REPORT NOW.
YES, IF YOU PLEASE.
REGARDING MAIHAMA AND
THE COWEN FAMILY.
I'M SURE YOU'RE ALREADY PRETTY
FAMILIAR WITH PRINCESS RAYNESHIA
AND HER GRANDFATHER,
LORD SERJIAD?
FOR THE RECORD, LORD SERJIAD
HAS TAKEN A RECENT INTEREST
IN SEAWEED SALADS AND
BEAN‐FILLED PANCAKES.
HE ALSO DRINKS A WARM GLASS
OF MILK BEFORE BED, MILORD.
[SHIROE] UH... NOW
WAIT A SECOND...!
HOW DID YOU GET THIS
INFORMATION?!
PLEASE TELL ME YOU DIDN'T
BREAK INTO THE PALACE! UH...!
[AKATUSKI] RELAX...
RAYNESHIA TOLD ME!
[SHIROE] UH...?
GIRL POWER...
IT SHOULD NOT BE UNDERESTIMATED.
[SHIROE]
UHHH... "GIRL POWER"?
IT'S NOT FAIR TO DOUBT MY
FRIENDSHIPS WITH OTHER WOMEN!
[SHIROE]
I DON'T THINK I EVER DID.
I CAN BE EXTREMELY
FEMININE WHEN NEEDED.
YOU DON'T SAY?
I EVEN ATTENDED THE GIRL'S CLUB!
UH, OKAY...
SO? WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK IT'S REALLY
NICE AKATSUKI,
IT'S A GOOD THING YOU FINALLY
MADE SOME MORE FRIENDS.
[AKATSUKI] I KNOW, RIGHT?
KIND OF ENJOYING IT!
ANYWAY, THE REST OF THE REPORT.
RESPECTED AS A WISE RULER,
LORD SERJIAD IS THE CURRENT
HEAD OF THE COWEN FAMILY
AND 60 YEARS OLD.
HIS WIFE HAS ALREADY PASSED.
IN HIS YOUNGER YEARS, HE LED
THE ROYAL KNIGHTS
AGAINST MONSTERS... UH?
MY LORD, WHAT'S WRONG?
[SHIROE] HUH?
YOUR FACE IS ALL WRINKLED
WITH WORRY AGAIN.
UH, YEAH...
SOMETHING'S UP.
[SHIROE] THE CHIEF ISN'T
MAKING HIS USUAL REPORTS.
[AKATSUKI] NO?
THAT'S NOT LIKE HIM.
[SHIROE] THAT AND I CAN'T USE
THE LINK TO REACH HIM, NOW.
HAS THIS BEEN A PROBLEM BEFORE?
[SHIROE]
NOT REALLY, NO.
IF I CAN'T REACH HIM,
HOW CAN MINORI AND
THE OTHERS REACH ME?
(VOICE CHAT INTERFERENCE)
[SERARA] I CAN'T GET
ANYONE TO PICK UP.
[MINORI] ME TOO. I WAS HOPING TO
GET SOME ADVICE ABOUT SOMETHING.
[MINORI, THINKING]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HOW LONG HAS THE
LINK BEEN DOWN?!
UH...?
[MINORI] MAYBE THAT'S IT.
[SERARA] UH...?
[DARIELLA] INSTANT REBIRTH
CARRIES A PRICE WITH IT...
IT SUPPOSEDLY UPSETS THE VOICE
OF THE MIND IN ADVENTURERS.
MAYBE IT'S DISRUPTING
THE TELEPATHIC LINK...
HUH? WHAT?
THAT PORTABLE
SHRINE OF THEIRS...
MAYBE IT'S CAUSING
THE BLACKOUT.
[SERARA] PERHAPS WE COULD JUST
ASK THE KNIGHTS ABOUT IT?
I KNOW THEY'RE SPOOKY‐LOOKING,
BUT THEY CAN'T BE BAD IF THEY'RE
PROTECTING VILLAGES, RIGHT?
[MINORI]
MM‐HM! ULP...
‐IF ONLY NYANTA WERE HERE.
‐IF ONLY SHIROE WERE HERE.
[BOTH] HUH?!
(GIGGLING)
NOW THAT'S FUNNY...
DIDN'T WE ALL SAY WE
WERE GONNA DO THIS WITHOUT
THE OTHERS HELPING US?
YEAH, WE DID.
[DARIELLA] I'M NOT
SURE WHAT I'VE DONE,
BUT IT HURTS TO THINK
THAT YOU HATE ME.
[TOYA] I SAID I DIDN'T.
THEN WHAT IS IT ABOUT
MY SMILING THAT UPSETS YOU?
[TOYA] (BREATH) HUH?
[TOYA] OH!
OH MY GOD...!
[MINORI] SO WHAT DO YOU
THINK MISS ROE2'S GONNA DO?
[SERARA] THAT'S A GOOD
QUESTION, MINORI!
[MINORI] WELL, I MEAN SHE
SAID SHE'S GOING TO IKOMA...
[SERARA] WITH MISS
DARIELLA, MAYBE? HMMM...
[MINORI] ISUZU STILL HASN'T
COME OUT OF HER ROOM TODAY.
[SERARA] MAYBE SHE'S
ALREADY MISSING ROE2.
[MINORI] SHE SAID SHE WAS
GONNA KEEP TRAVELLING
WITH US AS LONG AS SHE COULD.
WHICH MEANS SHE'LL BE NEEDING
TO SPLIT OFF FROM US HERE.
SO WE'RE GONNA HAVE
TO FIND A CARPENTER
TO GET OUR SUMMONING
FLUTE WORKING AGAIN.
(SERARA GASPS)
[MINORI] WHAT IS IT, SERARA?
[SERARA] I DON'T LIKE THE LOOKS
OF THAT CLOUD. [MINORI] HUH?
[SERARA] I'M NOT SURE WHAT IT
IS, BUT I DON'T LIKE IT...
(WOLF‐CHAN GROWLING)
[MINORI] I DON'T
THINK THAT'S A CLOUD.
(GROWL/ROAR)
A WYVERN SWARM!
HUH?!
[MINORI] AND THEY'RE
COMING RIGHT AT US!
[TOYA] THIS IS BAD, REALLY BAD.
MISS DARIELLA, YOU NEED
TO TAKE COVER SOMEWHERE!
WHAT ABOUT YOU? HOW'RE YOU
GOING TO STAY SAFE, TOYA?!
[TOYA, THINKING] WHAT IN
THE WORLD IS GOING ON?!
(ROAR)
[MINORI]
HOW POWERFUL ARE THEY?
FORTY‐TWO! FORTY‐SIX!
FORTY‐THREE! FIFTY!
WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO, MINORI?
FIVE OF US AND
HUNDREDS OF THEM...?
I DON'T THINK WE'D
STAND A CHANCE!
[TOYA]
MINORI! SERARA!
[MINORI]
TOYA!
[TOYA] WE GOTTA GET
OUT OF THE VILLAGE!
WE CAN'T PUT ALL THESE PEOPLE
IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS!
[MINORI] YES, BUT...
[TOYA] COME ON!
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE, OKAY?
GOT IT!
(PANTING)
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] THE
ODYSSEY KNIGHTS STAND BEFORE A
FLIGHT OF WYVERNS
ATTACKING THE VILLAGE.
THEY'RE NOT FIGHTING
TO PROTECT ANYONE;
THEY'RE FIGHTING TO EXPERIENCE
DEATH OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
TOYA, MINORI, AND SERARA STAND
BY AND WATCH IN HORROR,
WHILE RUDY AND ISUZU
ENGAGE THE ONSLAUGHT!
THIS TIME, THEY WILL
BATTLE THE GODS!
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.