(FESTIVAL CHATTER)
[MARIELLE] WOW, THEY'VE
REALLY GOTTEN INTO THE SPIRIT!
[HENRIETTA]
WELL, TODAY IS VALENTINE'S DAY.
WELL I'M GONNA GO ALL OUT!
(EXHALE)
[SERARA]
JEEZ, THAT'S EXPENSIVE.
TODAY'S LIKE PRICE
GOUGE CITY OUT HERE!
I GUESS EVERYONE'S TRYING TO BUY
SOMETHING FOR VALENTINE'S DAY.
[NYANTA] WELL, IF IT ISN'T
MY GIRL, SERARA.
MISTER CAT!
IS EVERYTHING
ALL RIGHT, BABY?
[SERARA]
YEAH! IT'S JUST... I, UH...
[NYANTA] LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE
EYEBALLIN' SOME COCONIA.
AND, LET ME TELL YOU, THIS
FRUIT RIGHT HERE IS SO GOOD,
THEY USE IT IN PIES, CAKES,
DRINKS, EVERYTHING SWEET, MMM!
[SERARA]
WOW! THAT'S REALLY AMAZING!
[SERARA, THINKING]
I ALREADY KNEW THAT...
AND THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
HAVE A SUPERSTITION
THAT THEY ABSOLUTELY
POSITIVELY SWEAR BY, HM.
IF YOU SERVE IT TO YOUR
SWEETHEART ON FEBRUARY 14TH,
TRUE LOVE WILL BLOOM!
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S VALENTINE'S DAY BACK
IN THE REAL WORLD, TOO, HUH?
YES! YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT!
WELL, 'SCUSE ME...
I SUDDENLY REMEMBERED
SOME CHORES!
GOTTA GO! GOTTA GO!
(CHUCKLE)
(SLURP)
[TOYA]
MASTER NAOTSUGU...
CAN YOU HELP ME PRACTICE
SOME TANK POSITIONS?!
[NAOTSUGU]
HUH? OH, SORRY, LITTLE DUDE...
I GOT SOMETHING
GOING ON TODAY!
[TOYA]
WHAT?!
YOU GOT SOMETHING "GOING ON"
WITH MARIELLE.
THAT'S RIGHT... AFTER ALL,
IT'S VALENTINE'S DAY TODAY!
HUH?
UH?
OH YEAH, IT IS. Y'KNOW
THAT REMINDS ME...
OF AN INSANE REQUEST
ASKED OF ME AGES AGO.
I BET YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT KANAMI! (GIGGLE)
[SHIROE] UH?
[TETORA] OH, COME ON NOW!
BOTH OF YOU WERE MEMBERS OF THE
TOTALLY LEGENDARY
DEBAUCHERY TEA PARTY, RIGHT?!
SO WAS I. EVER HEARD OF
PERSONAL SPACE? (PUSHED)
[TETORA]
FROM WHAT I HEARD,
KANAMI DIDN'T JUST
RUN THE PARTY.
SHE WAS, LIKE, SUPER SEXY AND
WAY POPULAR WITH ALL THE GUYS!
AND I ALSO HEARD SHE WAS
A LITTLE OLDER THAN YOU!
ZAT RIGHT?
C'MON, LOVERBOY! FESS UP!
SHE WAS YOUR
SWEETHEART, RIIIGHT?!
AND YOU'RE STILL
IN LOVE WITH HER!
[SHIROE] UH...!
THAT'S KIND OF A STRETCH...
WE DIDN'T HAVE A RELATIONSHIP.
[TETORA] REALLY? BUT I BET YOU
STILL LIKE HER, RIGHT?
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] WAIT!
WHO ON EARTH IS THIS WOMAN?
MY LORD IS USUALLY
CALM AND COLLECTED,
BUT SHE'S CLEARLY
GOT HIM FLUSTERED!
DOES HE HAVE FEELINGS FOR HER?
[MINORI, THINKING]
ANOTHER ANOTHER WOMAN?!
COOL IT, WILLYA?
YOU NEED TO PULL YOUR NOSE
OUT OF HIS BUSINESS.
STOP PESTERING HIM ALREADY!
EHEH! YOU KNOW REAL GIRLS
ALWAYS GOSSIP ABOUT SOMETHING!
[TOYA] DUDE! I CAN'T BELIEVE
MASTER NAOTSUGU
HASN'T FIGURED ALL THIS OUT YET!
[TOYA] I MEAN, YOU DO KNOW
THAT TETORA'S A GUY, RIGHT?
[RUDY]
YES, YES, OF COURSE.
I THOUGHT IT WAS
OBVIOUS BY NOW...
DO YOU THINK WE
SHOULD GO TELL HIM?
[RUDY] I'M STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE SOMETHING OUT...
DO I CALL HIM "MISS" TETORA?
OR DO I CALL HIM "MR." TETORA?
YEAH I'M STILL TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHETHER I'M GONNA
CALL HIM "BIG BRO" OR
"BIG SIS" OR WHATEVER.
[TETORA] AND WHAT'RE YOU
TWO NOSIES TALKING ABOUT?!
HEY! WE REALLY WEREN'T TALKING
ABOUT ANYTHING, BIG BRO‐STER!
[TETORA] WHAT...?
[TOYA] UH, SORRY!
MISS... TER... MA'AM, MISTER...
[TETORA] HUH?
HONESTLY WE'RE STUCK IN A
LITTLE BIT OF A MORAL CONUNDRUM
OVER HOW WE SHOULD
ADDRESS YOU PROPERLY.
LUCKY FOR YOU THERE'S ONLY
ONE ANSWER!
ALL YOU REALLY NEED TO SAY
IS TETORA‐BABY!
[BOTH] (NERVOUS LAUGHTER)
[TOYA] KAY...
[ISUZU]
UGH...
WELL THAT DOESN'T LOOK RIGHT...
[NYANTA] NOW THERE'S
A SIGHT, HM.
[ISUZU] UH... OH...
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
I ACTUALLY SAW YOU HERE?
[ISUZU]
UH, IT'S BEEN A WHILE.
WELL I'M BETTING IT'S
A SPECIAL OCCASION.
[ISUZU]
HERE'S THE THING...
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO MAKE A
DESSERT WITH THESE BUT UH...
[NYANTA] OH, MY GOODNESS,
MORE COCONIA FRUITS.
YEAH! AND IT'S NOT LIKE I'M
TRYING SOMETHING CRAZY.
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE A
LITTLE SOMETHING SPECIAL
THAT RUDY MIGHT LIKE.
[NYANTA]
OH REALLY... MMM.
[ISUZU] BUT I DON'T HAVE
THE CHEF SUBCLASS SO...
WHY DON'T WE TRY IT AGAIN
AND SEE IF WE CAN ACTUALLY MAKE
SOMETHING EDIBLE THIS TIME.
HUH? BUT IT'S JUST GONNA
TURN INTO A PUDDLE AGAIN
IF I PUT MY HANDS ON IT.
I HAVE JUST THE ITEM
FOR THE OCCASION, BABY!
THE NEWLYWED WIFE'S APRON DRESS!
A MASTER CHEF
ALWAYS HAS A SPARE.
ALRIGHT!
THE APRON DRESS WILL
LOWER YOUR BARDING
STATISTICS FOR A WHILE...
ON THE OTHER HAND YOU'LL
GET THE ABILITY TO WHIP UP
A BUNCH OF DELICIOUS GOODIES!
[ISUZU]
THIS IS FANTASTIC!
WITH THIS APRON, EVEN I CAN
MAKE AN AMAZING DESSERT!
[NYANTA]
WOW, BABY... LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
SO UH, WHAT WERE YOU DOING
WALKING AROUND WITH
AN APRON DRESS THINGY.
IT WAS AN ITEM DROP
ON A QUEST.
AND NOW... Y'SEE...
IN CASE YOU'RE FEELING JUST A
LITTLE BIT RUSTY IN THE KITCHEN.
I'VE GOT AN EASY PASTRY RECIPE
THAT YOU CAN DO QUICKLY.
PEEL THE COCONIA FRUIT
AND CUT IT INTO HALF‐CIRCLES,
AND PUT THEM INTO BOILING WATER.
ONCE YOU CAN GET A SKEWER
INTO 'EM NICE AND EASY,
GO AHEAD AND TRANSFER 'EM
INTO A BOWL.
AND CRUSH THEM WITH
A WOODEN SPATULA
WHILE THEY'RE STILL
HOT AND GOOEY.
STRAIN IT NOW AND THEY'LL HAVE
THAT VELVETY TEXTURE
EVERYONE JUST DIES FOR.
OH I LOVE IT!
[NYANTA] ADD SUGAR, EGG YOLK,
WHIPPING CREAM AND BUTTER,
IN THAT ORDER AND THEN MIX WELL.
ONCE IT COOLS DOWN,
ROLL THE DOUGH BETWEEN YOUR
PALMS TO SHAPE THE PASTRIES.
BRUSH SOME MORE EGG YOLK
OVER THEM TO GET 'EM SHINY.
AND PLACE THEM IN THE
SALAMANDER‐PREHEATED OVEN.
ONCE THEY'VE BAKED TO
A GOLDEN BROWN...
YOU'LL HAVE MOCK SWEET POTATO
COCONIA PASTRIES! MHMMM!
AHHHH! IT SMELLS GREAT!
I'VE GOTTA FIND RUDY
AND GIVE THESE TO HIM
WHILE THEY'RE STILL WARM!
THANKS SO MUCH CHIEF,
YOU'RE THE BEST!
WELL NOW, I'M QUITE SURE
THIS DAY ISN'T OVER
MIGHT AS WELL CLEAN UP
FOR THE NEXT GIRL.
[MINORI, THINKING]
SINCE IT IS VALENTINE'S,
I'D REALLY LIKE TO GIVE SHIROE
SOME KIND OF PRESENT.
JEEZ! I'D BE TOTALLY EMBARRASSED
IF HE TOOK IT THE
WRONG WAY, THOUGH...
UH‐UH! I'VE GOT TO
GET HIM SOMETHING
OR IT'D BE REALLY WEIRD.
I MEAN, I'VE GOTTA SHOW HIM
MY APPRECIATION TODAY, RIGHT?
SHE WAS YOUR SWEETHEART,
RIIIGHT!?
AND YOU'RE STILL
IN LOVE WITH HER!
[SHIROE]
HUH?!
(WATER SLOSHING)
(SLIME GROANS)
(ANNOYED) KANAMI...
MMM... UH?
[TETORA] YOO‐HOO!
HEY TETORA, DO YOU
NEED ME FOR SOMETHING?
I'VE GOT SOME
INFORMATION FOR YOU,
YOU WANNA KNOW ABOUT KANAMI?
WHAT... ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
COME ON! IT'S SO
OBVIOUS, AKATSUKI.
I'VE GOT THE DIRT ON HER
AND I KNOW YOU WANT IT!
(ANNOYED) OKAY. ASSUMING I WAS
INTERESTED, WHAT'S GOING ON?
[TETORA] (GIGGLE) CHECK IT OUT.
[AKATSUKI] HMMMM?
[TETORA] THIS IS CALLED A
"COCONIA FRUIT."
AND PEOPLE SAY THEY HAVE
TOTALLY AWESOME POWERS
ON VALENTINE'S DAY.
SO WHAT ARE THESE "POWERS"
SUPPOSED TO BE?
I DUNNO, YOU CAN JUST LOOK AT
THE FLAVOR TEXT TO FIND OUT.
[AKATSUKI] "COCONIA FRUIT: THE
PLANT IS NATIVE TO THE SOUTH.
IT CAN BE USED IN A WIDE VARIETY
OF DISHES, FROM FOOD TO DRINKS.
ON VALENTINE'S DAY,
FEEDING THIS TO SOMEONE
MAY REVEAL WHAT'S
TRULY IN THEIR HEART."
HMM? SO WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
WELL YOU KNOW HOW
FLAVOR TEXT
IS ACTUALLY INFLUENCING
HOW THINGS WORK, DON'T YOU?
THINK ABOUT THAT
FOR A MINUTE...!
YOU CAN FIND OUT WHO
SHIROE'S IN LOVE WITH!
[AKATSUKI] HUH?
SO DO YOU WANNA SIT AROUND
AND JUST WONDER ABOUT IT?
OR WOULD YOU RATHER GIVE HIM
A LITTLE NUDGE
WITH SOME COCONIA FRUIT
AND FIND OUT
WHAT'S GOING ON FOR YOURSELF?
TOODLES!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
COCONIA FRUIT...
[MINORI, ANGRILY]
COCONIA FRUIT...!
[HENRIETTA] I KNOW THE
APRON'S HELPING YOU...
BUT SERIOUSLY...
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN THIS
AMBITIOUS IN THE KITCHEN?
THIS IS THE DAY
EVERY GIRL STEPS UP
AND DOES HER BEST
FOR HER MAN!
[HENRIETTA]
OH GOOD GRIEF MARIELLE?
HUH... JUST WHO IS SHE
BAKING FOR, ANYWAY?
[ISSAC]
IT'S BEEN ABOUT A MONTH
SINCE WE LOST THE MAGIC CIRCLE
AROUND THE CITY.
WE WERE EXPECTING
ALL HELL TO BREAK LOOSE.
[SHIROE] AKIHABARA HAS
ALWAYS TENDED TO ATTRACT
HIGH‐LEVEL ADVENTURERS...
ANY MONSTERS WITH DECENT
INTELLIGENCE STAY AWAY FROM US.
AND OUR PATROLS ARE HANDLING
ANY THAT CHOOSE OTHERWISE.
[ISSAC] NO ONE'S REPORTED
ANY PLAYER KILLINGS
TO THE ROUND TABLE
SINCE THEN, EITHER.
EINS WAS PULLING HIS
GREEN HAIR OUT
THINKING THERE WAS GONNA BE
ANOTHER RASH OF MURDERS.
EVERYTHING'S BEEN
GOING PRETTY WELL.
WE'RE STILL GONNA HAVE TO
KEEP AN EYE ON THINGS
TO PROTECT
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND...
IT'S NOT SAFE FOR
THEM OUT THERE.
YEAH, WE'VE GOT THAT COVERED:
ALL OUR BEST RAID GUILDS ARE
ROTATING THROUGH GUARD DUTY.
THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR...
BY THE WAY, WHICH
GUILD'S ON DUTY TODAY?
THAT WOULD BE
THE WEST WIND.
HUH?
'COURSE I HAVEN'T
NOTICED 'EM OUT THERE.
I KINDA GET THE FEELING
WE WON'T BE SEEING MUCH OF THEM.
HM?
(SQUEALING GIRLS)
MASTER SOJIRO, PLEASE
ACCEPT MY FEELINGS FOR YOU!
HEY! I DON'T THINK SO!
I'M AHEAD OF YOU!
[NAZNA] COULD YOU PLEASE
CALM DOWN AND STAY IN LINE!
[SOJIRO] THANK YOU!
I PROMISE I'LL SAVOR EVERY BITE!
[DOLCHE] THAT'S ENOUGH
[GIRL] MASTER SOJI, THANK YOU!
[NAZNA] THAT'S RIGHT!
KEEP IT MOVING! WHO'S NEXT?!
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
NO ONE'S REPORTED SEEING
MASTER KRUSTY SINCE
THE INCIDENT WITH MISA.
OH HONESTLY!
THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT
THAT MONSTER IS UP TO,
NO MATTER WHERE HE IS!
BUT I'M SURE IF HE FEELS LIKE IT
HE'LL JUST WALTZ THROUGH THAT
DOOR AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED.
[ELISSA] PRINCESS RAYNESHIA!
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
YOU'RE STILL MILLING AROUND
IN THOSE BAGGY OLD PAJAMAS?
IT'S REALLY LATE IN
THE DAY FOR THAT!
WELL I DON'T HAVE ANY
"ROYAL" THINGS TO DO TODAY!
[ELISSA]
THAT'S NOT THE POINT, NOW...
CLOTHES CAN SET YOUR FRAME OF
MIND FOR THE REST OF THE DAY.
ANYWAY, ALL THE VENDORS WERE
SOLD OUT OF COCONIA,
SO I USED A LITTLE REPLACEMENT.
I THINK YOU MIGHT
LIKE THIS INSTEAD.
OH I'LL GIVE
IT A TRY THEN.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
UGH,
IS THAT MAN EVEN TAKING HIS
OATH OF KNIGHTHOOD SERIOUSLY?
UH! OH WOW THIS
IS REALLY AMAZING!
[AKANEYA]
HOW IS IT WORKING FOR YOU?
[MISA] A LITTLE STRANGE,
BUT I'M GETTING USED TO IT.
[RIEZE]
THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
[AKANEYA] WE CAN MAKE SOME
IMPROVEMENTS DOWN THE ROAD.
[RODERICK] I'LL DO WHAT I CAN
TO FIND MATERIALS
THAT WON'T PUT AS MUCH
STRAIN ON YOUR BODY.
[AKANEYA] THE RADIO MARKET
AND RODERICK MERCHANT GUILDS
ARE COLLABORATING
ON THE RESEARCH.
DON'T WORRY; I'M SURE
WE'LL WORK THIS OUT!
[MISA] I APPRECIATE ALL
YOUR HELP... BUT STILL...
WHERE DO YOU THINK MY ARM WENT
AFTER GETTING CAUGHT
IN THE VORTEX?
[AKANEYA] NORMALLY THERE
ARE HEALING SPELLS
THAT WOULD'VE
REGENERATED YOUR ARM...
SO I CAN ONLY FIGURE THAT
WHATEVER HAPPENED TO YOU
AND KRUSTY
IS NOT PART OF
THE ORIGINAL PROGRAMMING
FOR THE GAME.
OTHER THAN THE FACT IT
DISAPPEARED WITH KRUSTY...
I GET THE FEELING IT'S STILL
IN THE SAME ZONE WITH HIM,
WHEREVER THAT MAY BE.
[AKANEYA] OBVIOUSLY, WE'VE NEVER
SEEN SOMETHING LIKE THIS BEFORE.
[RIEZE] YOU TRY TO
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
WHAT YOU SHOULD FOCUS ON NOW
IS YOUR RECOVERY.
I HAVE NO PROBLEM
PICKING UP THE SLACK FOR YOU
UNTIL LORD KRUSTY RETURNS.
[MISA]
OKAY... THANK YOU FOR THAT.
MY LORD...
[MINORI] NYANTA!
[NYANTA] HM?
(GRUNT)
I GUESS I OVERDID IT, BUT Y'KNOW
THEY WERE REALLY CHEAP!
[NYANTA, THINKING]
WHY DO I GET THE FEELING
THEY WERE NOT "CHEAP"?
[MINORI]
CHIEF!
YEAH, YEAH. I'M LISTENIN', BABY.
SINCE I ALREADY GOT
A BUNCH OF COCONIA.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO EXPRESS MY
GRATITUDE TO OUR GUILD MASTER
FOR THE WAY HE LOOKS AFTER US.
[NYANTA] MM‐HM...
IT'S... NOT WHAT YOU THINK!
IT'S NOT RELATED TO
VALENTINES AT ALL! UH?!
OH I THINK YOU'VE MAKE YOUR
FEELINGS PERFECTLY CLEAR.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE CAN WHIP UP
IN THE KITCHEN, ALL RIGHT?
THANK YOU CHIEF!
[AKATSUKI] EXCUSE ME,
AKATSUKI, REPORTING BACK
FROM A QUEST
THAT ALSO DOUBLED
AS TRAINING, SIR!
AS IT HAPPENS, THE REWARD WAS
NONE OTHER THAN COCONIA FRUIT.
AS SUCH I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW
IF YOU WOULD TEACH ME...
THAT SEEMS LIKE A STRANGE
REWARD ITEM FOR A QUEST.
[AKATSUKI] IT'S A PRESENT
FOR MY LORD! HUH?
[AKATSUKI]
MINORI...!
MISS AKATSUKI...?
(BREATH)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
LOOKS LIKE SHE GOT HER HANDS
ON SOME COCONIA AS WELL.
[MINORI, THINKING] SHE WENT
OUT LOOKING FOR THEM, TOO?!
NO! WE'RE TRYING TO DO
THE SAME THING!
[NYANTA, THINKING]
THIS IS NOT GOOD, MYAH.
NEVER HAS THERE BEEN
SUCH A GRAVE THREAT
TO THE UNITY OF LOG HORIZON!
[TETORA, THINKING]
OH, GOD! THIS IS SO GOOD,
IT'S LIKE I'VE GOT MY
VERY OWN SOAP OPERA.
THAT'S MY CUE!
HELLO!
SINCE THE TWO OF YOU ARE
AFTER THE SAME THING...
WHY DON'T YOU TWO SETTLE IT
LIKE SOME SELF‐RESPECTING
FIRST CLASS LADIES!
GET TOGETHER AND MAKE
HIM SOMETHING NICE!
[BOTH]
TOGETHER, HUH?
I ACTUALLY THINK THAT
IDEA HAS A LOT OF MERIT,
BUT WE HAVE A LITTLE
PROBLEM, BABY.
I'VE ONLY GOT ONE APRON TO WEAR.
(GIGGLE)
WELL! LOOK AT WHAT MARIELLE
LEFT LAYING AROUND! UH‐WHOA!
[AKATSUKI]
NOW LET'S GET STARTED.
MASTER, PLEASE INSTRUCT ME.
[TETORA] A‐LA CUISINE!
[MINORI]
YEAH. ME TOO!
[NYANTA]
MIGHT AS WELL GET STARTED.
[TETORA] HURRAY!
LET'S HEAR IT FOR THE MAIDENS!
JUST REMEMBER THAT THE WORLD
STILL REVOLVES AROUND ME,
ALL RIGHT YOU GUYS?!
[ISUZU]
THIS IS SO WEIRD!
WHERE ON EARTH COULD RUDY BE?
[ISUZU]
MMM...
ALL RIGHT. FINE!
GUESS I'LL GO HOME...
SORRY I KEPT YA!
HEY, NAOTSUGU!
YOU KNOW, UH...
TODAY'S VALENTINES...
[NAOTSUGU]
UH, YEAH.
EHEH! HANG ON A SEC...
OKAY, NOW. HERE YOU GO!
THEY'RE HARD CANDIES.
[NAOTSUGU] THANKS. AHEM,
(DEEPER VOICE) THANKS.
[SHORYU]
AGGHHH!
[MARIELLE]
NAOTSUGU, WELL...
TO BE HONEST, SOMETHING'S
BEEN ON MY MIND A LOT LATELY.
THE NEW GIRL IN YOUR GUILD.
UH... SHE'S KIND OF ADORABLE
AND CUTE AND GROSS...
BUT YOU KNOW... ANYWAY...
I GUESS I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO ASK YOU THIS FOR AWHILE.
[NAOTSUGU] MMM?! UHH...
[MARIELLE] WHAT DOES IT FOR YOU,
NAOTSUGU? WHAT DO YOU LOVE?
[NAOTSUGU] OH... I... LOVE...!
[MARIELLE] HUH?
[MARIELLE, THINKING]
HE LOVES WHAT?
[NAOTSUGU] P‐PAN‐!
[MARIELLE] HUH...
[NAOTSUGU]
‐N‐! YAHHH!
[MARIELLE] NAOTSUGU,
ARE YOU OKAY?! WHAT HAPPENED?
[SHORYU] ARE THE ROYAL GUARDS
BACK IN SERVICE OR SOMETHING?
UH, MISS AKATSUKI, DID YOU
JUST DISAPPEAR FOR A SECOND?
I'M A NINJA.
[MARIELLE]
REALLY!
HOW BIG OF A JERK CAN YOU BE?!
ALL HE HAD TO DO IS
JUST SAY LIKE...
"THAT QUESTION'S JUST A
LITTLE TOO PERSONAL."
HUH?
SHORYU...?
HEY THERE...
OH, HEY. WOULD YOU
LIKE SOME OF THIS?
I WOUND UP WITH A
LITTLE BIT EXTRA. HERE.
(GASP) ARE YOU SURE?!
[MARIELLE]
SEE YA AROUND.
GOD, SHE MAKES ME SO HAPPY!
[NAOTSUGU] WE'RE BAAACK!
[SHIROE] HELLO?
WHAT IN THE HELL WAS
THAT ANYWAY, MAN?!
WHAT WAS WHAT?
SOMEONE CAME OUTTA NOWHERE
AND KICKED ME IN THE HEAD!
[NYANTA]
WELCOME HOME, MYAH.
[SHIROE] HUH?
[NAOTSUGU] HM?
[NAOTSUGU]
WHOA!
AWESOME! I'VE GOTTA TRY‐ AH!
[AKATSUKI]
NO, THIS ISN'T FOR YOU!
ALL OF THESE SWEETS ARE
A VALENTINE'S DAY GIFT
FOR THE GUILD MASTER.
[SHIROE]
ALL OF IT?
[NYANTA]
THAT'S RIGHT.
THE LADIES HERE WORKED TOGETHER
TO PREPARE SOME PASTRIES
SPECIALLY FOR YOU, SHIROE‐ECCHI.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT?
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY MADE
EVERYTHING FROM SCRATCH.
THAT THEY DID. I MADE SURE
THEY HAD THE PROPER ATTIRE,
THE RIGHT EQUIPMENT,
AND I SHOWED THEM HOW TO FIND
THEIR WAY AROUND THE KITCHEN.
AND I CHEERED THEM ON!
[TETORA] NOW C'MERE, LOVERBOY!
[SHIROE] HUH? WHA... WAUUUGHHH!
[TETORA] TAKE A SEAT!
[SHIROE] GWAH! OWAH...
(STARING)
[SHIROE, THINKING]
HOW DID I END UP IN THIS MESS?!
I STILL HAVE CAKE TRAUMA
FROM THE LAST TIME.
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD, PLEASE HURRY.
PLEASE ENJOY
THE CAKE WE MADE!
RIGHT, SURE THING.
REALLY APPRECIATE IT...
(CHOMP)
(HOLDING BREATH)
(CHEWS, SWALLOW)
[SHIROE]
THIS IS...
AMAZING! (HYPER MUNCHING)
ALL RIGHT!
AREN'T YOU GLAD HE
LIKES IT, AKATSUKI?
YEAH!
WAUUUGGHHHH!
[BOTH]
HUH?
MM?
SHOWTIME!
UHH...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
THIS IS IT...!
[MINORI, THINKING]
THE COCONIA FRUIT'S SPECIAL
VALENTINE'S DAY POWER...!
IT'S TIME TO FIND OUT WHERE
HIS TRUE LOVE REALLY LIES!
ASK HIM! ASK HIM QUICK!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
OKAY, FINE.
SO WHAT EXACTLY
SHOULD I ASK HIM?
[MINORI, THINKING] WHAT IF
SHIROE IS IN LOVE WITH AKATSUKI?
I'M NOT SURE I
WANT TO KNOW THAT!
I CAN'T.
I'M TOO SCARED TO ASK!
WHAT WOULD I DO IF
MY LORD SAID KANAMI?
AND WHO IS THIS
KANAMI ANYWAY?
NEVERMIND.
I HAVE NO QUESTIONS
FOR SHIROE.
[ISUZU] I CAN'T FIND
RUDY ANYWHERE!
HE'S NOT AT ANY OF
OUR USUAL SPOTS.
AFTER ALL THE TRAINING
WE DID TODAY...
I AM FREAKIN'
STAVING TO DEATH.
AH, I'M HUNGRY!
WHAT'S FOR DINNER TONIGHT?
WHAT'RE WE EATING?
I AM IN LOVE WITH
CURRY AND RICE!
(ALL GASPING)
(NYANTA CHUCKLES)
OKAY... TELL US SOMETHING
WE DON'T KNOW, PAL.
HUH? DID I SAY
SOMETHING JUST NOW?
HOW ABOUT THIS...
WHY DON'T WE MAKE UP
A GIANT BATCH OF CURRY.
OH WOW... YOU LIKE CURRY
BETTER THAN GIRLS, GUILD MASTER?
IT COULD'VE BEEN
A LOT WORSE...
THAT MIGHT HAVE
BEEN FOR THE BEST.
HUH?
AH!
[NYANTA]
YOU BROUGHT THESE FOR ME?
RIGHT! I SAW THEM FOR
SALE IN THE MARKETPLACE,
AND THOUGHT THEY
WERE REALLY CUTE.
[SERARA, THINKING] I WANTED
TO MAKE A TREAT FOR HIM...
... BUT THE COCONIA FRUIT
WERE ALL SOLD OUT.
AND NOBODY WAS SELLING
A NEWLYWED WIFE'S
APRON DRESS ANYWHERE.
(DEFLATED)
HMMM...
[NYANTA, THINKING]
THE STEMS ON THESE FLOWERS
ARE COVERED IN THORNS.
POOR GIRL WENT THE EXTRA MILE
TO PICK THESE FOR ME...
THAT WAS REALLY
THOUGHTFUL, LITTLE LADY.
AH... WE'RE GETTING
TOGETHER TONIGHT
FOR SOME CURRY AND RICE...
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME
JOIN US FOR DINNER,
SPEND SOME QUALITY TIME?
YEAH?! YOU
REALLY MEAN IT?
MOST DEFINITELY!
THANKS A LOT, MISTER CAT!
CAN I HELP IN THE KITCHEN?
[NYANTA]
OH YEAH. SURE. YOU BET.
AHHH... I CAN'T WAIT!
[RUDY]
I'M HOME!
[ISUZU]
RUDY... WHERE WERE YOU?
I COULDN'T FIND YOU ANYWHERE!
[RUDY] OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT!
I HAD SOME ERRANDS.
[ISUZU] WELL I GUESS IT'S OKAY.
THIS IS FOR YOU!
SO WHAT'S THIS?
IT LOOKS SWEET. OOOH...
[ISUZU] MOCK SWEET POTATO
COCONIA FRUIT PASTRIES!
[ISUZU] I KNOW WE HAVEN'T
HAD DINNER YET, BUT TRY ONE.
I MADE THEM MYSELF!
THAT WAS REALLY NICE OF YOU!
I'LL JUST HAVE TO GIVE IT A TRY.
OH WOW! THIS IS SO GOOD!
THANKS, ISUZU! (CHEWS)
AH! YOU REALLY LIKE IT?
[RUDY]
ACK!
WHAT'S UP? HEY... RUDY?
(RUDY GURGLES)
I LOVE EVERYBODY I'VE EVER
WORKED WITH IN THE GUILD!
[AKATSUKI]
OKAY, THEN.
GUESS THE CONFESSIONS AREN'T
LIMITED TO ROMANTIC LOVE.
MM...
(EXHALE) YEAH WELL,
I LOVE WORKIN' WITH
YOU TOO, RUDY!
[RUDY](LAUGHING)
WELL OF COURSE YOU DO!
[NAOTSUGU] SO WHAT'S
GOTTEN INTO THOSE DORKS?
[SHIROE]
I DUNNO...?
(FOOTSTEPS ECHOING)
[NUREHA]
SHIROE...
[INTIX]
PRINCESS NUREHA...
I SEE YOU'RE SLEEPING
ON THE FLOOR AGAIN...
WHAT IS IT, INTIX?
LET ME GUESS, YOU WERE
JUST THINKING ABOUT SHIROE.
UH?
I KNOW YOU WERE.
PLEASE DON'T TALK
TO ME ABOUT HIM.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
I'VE TOLD YOU MANY TIMES.
HE DOESN'T CARE FOR PEOPLE.
YOU CAN'T HAVE HIM.
HE ISN'T EVEN A REAL PLAYER.
HE'S NOTHING MORE THAN
HIGHLY COMPETENT NOISE.
THE MAN IS A TRAITOR
TO ALL HE STOOD FOR,
NO MATTER HOW CLEVER HE IS,
OR HOW HONORABLE HE ACTS.
BESIDES MY DEAR, YOU KNOW
HE CAN SEE RIGHT THROUGH YOU.
I MEAN, WHY WOULD HE WANT
SUCH A DIRTY LITTLE GIRL?
WHEN YOUR FILTH IS THE
ONLY THING ABOUT YOU
THAT DISTINGUISHES
YOU FROM ANYONE ELSE?
[NUREHA]
STOP IT!
HUH?
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOUR
EXISTENCE IS A LIE.
TAKE IT ALL AWAY AND
YOU ARE NEXT TO NOTHING.
HIDE THAT PRETTY LYING
FACE OF YOURS,
AND ALL THAT'S LEFT IS JUST
AN EMPTY, ROTTEN SHELL.
YOU'RE AN ABOMINATION.
FIT FOR NO ONE.
AND YOU DESERVE YOUR LONELINESS.
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
GET IT THROUGH YOUR HEAD.
YOU'RE NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
NOBODY WANTS YOU!
AND NOBODY EVER WILL!
YOU BETTER REMEMBER
THAT I'M THE ONLY ONE
THAT EVER WANTED YOU,
I'M THE ONLY ONE
WHO EVER WILL WANT YOU,
DESPITE YOUR
SOILED LITTLE HEART.
(NUREHA EXHALES)
(PINCHED)
[INTIX] YOU'RE THE PERFECT
PRINCESS FOR THE MASSES
TO VIEW FROM A DISTANCE,
LIKE A BIRD IN A CAGE.
IT'S TIME THAT YOU REALIZED...
THE DAYS OF YOUR PAMPERED
PRINCESS LIFE ARE LONG GONE.
REMEMBER WHAT OUR
GOALS ARE, MY DEAR...
YOU ARE GOING TO GATHER
A BUNCH OF BLIND BLATHERING
PUPPETS AND CREATE A KINGDOM.
AND THIS TIME I SHALL OBTAIN THE
YAMATO SERVER IN ITS ENTIRETY.
THAT WAS THE DEAL WE
STRUCK, WAS IT NOT?
YOU ARE GOING TO CREATE
A PLACE TO CALL YOUR OWN?
[NUREHA] UM... UH‐HUH.
[INTIX] THE TEN SEAT
CONFERENCE IS BEGINNING.
I'M SURE YOU
DON'T WANT TO MISS IT.
IT WOULDN'T BE THE SAME WITHOUT
EVERYONE'S FAVORITE FIGUREHEAD.
FEEL FREE TO JOIN US.
BUT YOU MAY WANT TO
CLEAN YOURSELF UP FIRST.
[NUREHA, THINKING]
YOU'RE WRONG, INTIX...
I HAVE SOMETHING FAR GREATER
THAN ANY PACT
I'VE MADE WITH YOU...
I'VE GOT HIM...
[SHIROE] I CAN GIVE YOU WHAT
YOU WANT MORE EFFECTIVELY
AS A FOE THAN I CAN AS A FRIEND.
SO WHENEVER YOU DECIDE
WHAT YOUR REASON IS...
I WILL BE YOUR ENEMY.
[NUREHA]
I MADE A PROMISE...
THE BIGGEST PROMISE
OF MY ENTIRE LIFE!
AND I'LL KEEP IT, FOR HIM...
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
THIS IS THE CHINA SERVER.
TURMOIL CAUSED BY
THE APOCALYPSE
HAS CONTINUED
ALL ACROSS THE WORLD.
AMIDST THAT CHAOS,
THERE IS SINGLE ADVENTURER
WHO GATHERS COMRADES AND
FIGHTS TO PROTECT OTHERS.
SHE WAS THE LEADER OF THE
VERY SAME DEBAUCHERY TEA PARTY
THAT SHIROE AND HIS FRIENDS
ONCE BELONGED.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.