[ARUMI]
HUH?
[DAIMONJI]
UH...?
[ARUMI]
PRINCESS... NUREHA?
[NUREHA]
UH...
[DAIMONJI]
MILADY... WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[ARUMI] DO YOU NEED YOUR
ESCORT TO GO WITH YOU?
SSSSHH!
[DARIELLA]
UWAH!
(GIGGLING AND HUMMING)
[MAN B] THANK GOD YOU GUYS
SHOWED UP BACK THERE!
[MAN A] YEAH, WE THOUGHT WE
WERE GONNA GET SOME BOARS,
BUT THEY WERE OGRES INSTEAD!
[RUDY]
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, GENTLEMEN!
AFTER ALL, WE'RE ADVENTURERS.
RESCUING PEOPLE IN DANGER
IS WHAT WE DO!
I'M SO GLAD YOU
DIDN'T GET HURT.
[TOYA]
YEAH, I'M OKAY.
BUT IT WAS OUR FRIEND
IN THE WAGON
WHO TOTALLY SAVED US ALL..
WE HAVE HER TO THANK.
[ROE2] UGGGHHH... GOD, THE SUN,
SOMEBODY TURN IT OFF!
[MINORI] HOW ARE YOU FEELING,
MISS ROE2? THIS OUGHTA HELP.
I'M SORRY, BUT YOU
GOTTA CLOSE THAT PLEASE?
I REALLY DON'T DO SUNLIGHT.
OH, YEAH. SURE.
THANK YOU,
I APPRECIATE IT.
OF COURSE.
(GULPING)
MM? WHAT'S WRONG?
[MINORI]
NOTHING! I WAS JUST WONDERING,
IS THAT A SPIRITUAL
CLOAK OF THE STARS?
YEAH! I'M SURPRISED
YOU KNEW.
WELL, MY TEACHER WEARS
ONE A LOT LIKE IT.
SO I GUESS HE'S
A MAGIC‐USER.
YEAH...
HE'S AN ENCHANTER.
THIS ROBE HAS SOME
PRETTY NICE STATS.
YOU CAN'T MAKE IT
LOSE IT'S POWER,
AND IT'S GOOD FOR
GENERAL USE...
AND IT'S GREAT
FOR LONG TRIPS.
YOU SOUND JUST LIKE
MASTER SHIROE, YOU KNOW?
HUH?
OH...! WHAT I MEAN, UH,
HOW DO I PUT THIS?
YOU JUST KINDA REMIND ME OF HIM.
THE WAY YOU TALK AND THE WAY
YOU DRESS ARE A LOT ALIKE!
OHH? OKAY, THEN.
LEMME TRY'N DO YOU NOW.
I'M GUESSING YOU'RE
A SHRINE MAIDEN!
THAT'S RIGHT!
OH YEAH! YOU NEED HEALING!
PLEASE DON'T...
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY.
ARE YOU SURE?
REMEMBER? I SAID
I WAS A VAMPIRE? AH?
OH. OKAY, I SEE!
HEALING SPELLS CAN ACTUALLY
HURT VAMPIRES, CAN'T THEY?
YEAH, AND I'M WAY
TOO WEAK ALREADY.
AND SO WHAT'RE YOU
DOING AFTER THIS?
HMMM...
UH...
[MINORI] MISS ROE2,
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
[ROE2]
HUH?
[MINORI]
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM...?
AND WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WELL WELL,
WHERE DID I COME FROM,
AND WHERE AM
I GOING, HUH?
THAT'S A LITTLE PERSONAL
COMING FROM SOMEONE
I JUST MET, YOU KNOW?
OH, SORRY!
I DIDN'T MEAN TO...! UH...
I KNOW YOU DIDN'T.
HMM?
[SERARA]
MINORI!
[MINORI]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[ISUZU]
LOOK AT THIS...!
IT MUST'VE HAPPENED
SOMETIME DURING THE FIGHT.
[SERARA] IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE CROISSANT AND DANISH
GOT HURT OR ANYTHING.
[MINORI]
SO HOW COULD THAT...?
OH, RIGHT!
EVEN STUFF LIKE THAT
HAS DURABILITY STATS.
WE COULD CALL THEM
IF WE FIXED IT, RIGHT?
WE WOULD NEED WOOD‐CRAFTING
SKILLS TO MAKE IT WORK.
YEAH WELL, FOR NOW WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT PUSHING THE WAGON
ALL THE WAY TO THE NEXT TOWN.
[SERARA]
WE'RE A LITTLE WORRIED
THAT MORE MONSTERS
MIGHT SHOW UP...
SO TOYA WENT AND TOLD THOSE
TWO PEOPLE OF THE LAND
THEY COULD COME WITH US.
[MINORI]
GOT IT.
[ISUZU] RUDY, WHY DON'T YOU
RIDE IN THE WAGON?
BARDS ARE STRONGER THAN
SORCERERS, YOU KNOW?
[RUDY]
OH, COME NOW...
WHAT KIND OF MAN WOULD I BE
IF I LET YOU DO THIS?
(GIGGLE)
[MAN A]
IT WAS REALLY BAD.
WE WERE JUST HEADED
DOWN THE MOUNTAINSIDE,
THEN WE FOUND OURSELVES
UP TO OUR NECKS IN OGRES!
[MAN B] YEAH, WELL.
I BET IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THEIR HOME
GETTING DESTROYED.
HUH? COULD THAT BE IT?
[MAN A]
WELL, IF YOU KEEP GOING WEST,
YOU'RE GONNA WIND UP AT
THE BOXROOT MOUNTAINS.
THERE'S A GORGEOUS LAKE
OUT THERE.
NOBLES RULE THE AREA,
BUT YOU'VE STILL GOTTA
WATCH OUT FOR MONSTERS.
[TOYA] AREN'T WE SUPPOSED
TO BE GOING THROUGH THERE?
[MINORI] YEAH...
[MAN B] THE MONSTERS AREN'T
THAT BIG OF A DEAL...
EVEN IF YOU SEE SOME,
THE ODYSSEY KNIGHTS'LL
TAKE CARE OF 'EM.
[MAN A] THAT'S RIGHT!
THOSE GUYS ARE THE BEST!
THEY'RE LIKE OUR HEROES! ALWAYS
RISKING THEIR LIVES FOR US.
[SERARA]
THEY RISK... THEIR LIVES?
YOU THINK MAYBE
THEY'RE SOMETHING LIKE
KRUSTY OR ISAAC'S GUYS?
MAYBE.
[MINORI, THINKING] BUT IF
I TOOK AN EDUCATED GUESS...
[SHIROE] THERE'S A GROUP
WE CALL THE "HOMESICK"
OR THE "ODYSSEY,"
A LOOSE ASSOCIATION OF PLAYERS
TRYING TO GET BACK HOME.
FROM WHAT I'VE HEARD,
THEY'RE WILLING TO TRY
JUST ABOUT ANYTHING
TO GET BACK.
AND BY THAT,
I MEAN "EVERYTHING."
THEY MIGHT END UP CAUSING
MORE TROUBLE THAN THEY FIX...
MMMM!
[MINORI, THINKING]
SHIROE DEFINITELY DIDN'T
CALL THEM "KNIGHTS." MAYBE
THEY'RE NOT THE SAME GROUP.
[ROE2] I OWE YOU GUYS
BIG TIME FOR THIS!
I PROBABLY WOULD'VE TURNED
INTO A PILE OF ASHES
IF I KEPT ON WALKING OUT
IN THE OPEN LIKE THAT.
[MINORI]
YEA, BUT YOU HELPED US!
[TOYA]
WE TOTALLY HELPED EACH OTHER.
THANKS FOR WAITING, GUYS!
THESE ARE FROM THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND WE HELPED.
IT'S THEIR WAY OF
PAYING US BACK.
[TOYA]
SOY SAUCE FOR ME!
[RUDY] I'M USING
WORCESTERSHIRE SAUCE!
[ISUZU] SAME HERE!
[SERARA] FOR A DISH LIKE THIS,
YA GOTTA HAVE MAYONNAISE.
OHH... KAY...
THIS IS ABSOLUTELY THE
BEST FLAVOR YOU CAN HAVE...!
GOURMET RANK B WORCESTERSHIRE.
OH‐KAY.
[SERARA]
OH, JUST THINK ABOUT IT!
I BET AN ADVENTURER CAME UP
WITH THIS BEEF BOWL DELIGHT!
OKAY...
[MINORI] ALRIGHT,
SO THIS IS SOY SAUCE
AND THAT'S WORCESTERSHIRE SAUCE.
[ROE2]
OKAY... (TITTERING AND GIGGLING)
[ISUZU]
WHOA. YOU'RE DOING BOTH OF THEM?
DIPLOMACY, MAYBE? SHE'S TRYING
TO AVOID A SAUCING DEBATE.
I SEE.
THE GOOEY BLACK ONE
IS WORCESTERSHIRE!
THE RUNNY BLACK ONE
IS SOY SAUCE! I GET IT NOW.
[SERARA] THE MAYO IS YUMMY,
TOO, YOU KNOW!
YOU MIND IF I ASK
YOU SOMETHING,
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM
BEFORE YOU MET US?
I MADE MY WAY HERE
FROM OOU CITY...
I'VE BEEN ON THE ROAD
ABOUT THREE MONTHS.
OOU CITY? THAT'S WHERE MASTER
SHIROE WENT ON HIS EXPEDITION.
[ROE2]
I ACTUALLY STARTED OUT
FROM A PLACE THAT WAS A
LITTLE FARTHER AWAY FROM THAT.
I USED CASTLING TO COVER
SUCH A LONG DISTANCE.
WHAT'S CASTLING...?
NEVER HEARD OF IT...
IT'S A SPELL THAT ALLOWS YOU TO
CHANGE PLACES WITH A COMPANION.
AND MISS ROE2 IS A MAGIC USER.
IN FACT, JUST THE OTHER DAY,
HONESTY STARTED USING CASTLING
TO RESEARCH HOW THEY COULD MAKE
FAIRY RINGS WORK FULL‐TIME.
[ISUZU] THAT'S AMAZING, MINORI!
YOU'VE REALLY GOT THIS DOWN!
[MINORI] HUH? I'M JUST REPEATING
WHAT MASTER SHIROE TOLD ME.
MISS ROE2, DOES THAT MEAN
YOU SWITCHED PLACES
WITH YOUR COMPANION?
I DON'T REALLY KNOW IF I'D
CALL HIM MY "COMPANION..."
I GUESS... HE'D BE MORE LIKE...
MORE LIKE MY OLDER BROTHER.
[ALL] BROTHER?
FOR THE TIME BEING,
I'M TRYING TO GET TO IKOMA.
UNTIL I DO, I'M STUCK WITH
THIS ANNOYING VAMPIRE
SUBCLASS OF MINE.
IS IT NOT LETTING YOU
TAKE QUESTS
THAT WOULD LET YOU
OVERWRITE IT?
THAT'S RIGHT...
GOTTA DO IT THE HARD WAY.
IF I COULD MEET THE JERK THAT
DECIDED ON THIS SUBCLASS,
I'D LOVE TO TAKE A BITE OUT
OF HIS THROAT OR SOMETHING!
"LOOKIE ME! I'M A VAMPIRE!"
[ISUZU] EHEH...
IT WAS KINDA USEFUL
ON THE MOON, I GUESS,
BUT WHATEVER MORON
CAME UP WITH IT
NEVER THOUGHT
I'D WIND UP HERE!
OMIGOD...
I HATE BEING A VAMPIRE!
(ROE2 ANGUISHED)
[MINORI] THE MOON...?
[TOYA]
IF I REMEMBER RIGHT,
ISN'T IKOMA NEAR MINAMI?
ALL RIGHT, SO HOW'RE WE
GONNA DO THE REST OF THIS?
[SERARA] UHHH...
[MINORI] FOR ONE THING WE
COULDN'T FIND ANYONE IN TOWN
WITH WOODCRAFTING SKILLS.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE A HARD TIME
FINISHING THIS TRIP
WITHOUT HORSES!
OH, COME ON.
LET'S JUST SUMMON SOME.
[ALL] HMM?!
[ROE2] HUH?
[TOYA] YOU CAN SUMMON HORSES,
BIG SIS ROE2?
HUH?!
BIG SIS ROE2?!
[ALL]
HUH?
[ROE2]
(LAUGHS) AHEM...
HEY KID... COULD YOU SAY
"BIG SIS" AGAIN FOR ME?
BIG SIS...
[ROE2]
(GASP) DO IT AGAIN!
BIG SIS...!
[ROE2]
(GASP) NOW YOU!
BIG SISTER ROE2.
AHHHH! (GIGGLE)
OH, I LOVE IT!
BIG SISTER!
I WISH... I REALLY WAS!
JUST TO HEAR YOU SAY IT, MAKES
ME THINK YOU'RE COUNTING ON ME.
AHA! I WANNA BECOME THE BIG
SISTER FIGURE IN YOUR LIVES!
I SHALL BE LOOKED UP TO
JUST LIKE YOUR OLDER SISTER!
I'LL GUIDE AND PROTECT YOU!
AND I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT I'M GONNA DO!
I SHALL SUMMON A HERD
OF AMAZING HORSES
THE LIKES OF WHICH
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN!
AND IN RETURN,
YOU SHALL PARADE ME AROUND
AS YOUR BIG SISTER! DEAL?
[ALL]
YEAH... THAT'S FINE...
HMPH! OH, GOD... TOO MUCH SUN!
(RELIEVED)
[MINORI]
DOESN'T THIS FEEL GREAT?
[SERARA] I KNOW ADVENTURERS
DON'T NEED TO TAKE BATHS,
BUT THIS IS REALLY AWESOME.
OUR WOUNDS HEAL FAST, AND THE
SYSTEM HELPS TO KEEP US CLEAN...
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
THAT BEATS A GOOD SOAK!
[BOTH]
AHHH! HMMM...
OH, YEAH! WE MIGHT HAVE
TROUBLE NAVIGATING
OUR WAY THROUGH THE
BOXROOT MOUNTAINS AHEAD.
RUDY SAID IT'S ROUGH.
[MINORI] IS THAT RIGHT?
YEAH. HE'S PRETTY WELL‐TRAVELED
AND KNOW THAT KINDA STUFF.
OH HE DOES, HUH?
YOU GUYS ARE SO CUTE.
HOW'RE THINGS WITH YOU TWO?
UH... WAIT WHAT?
HE'S JUST LIKE
MY LITTLE PUPPY DOG.
YEAH RIGHT!
IT'S SO OBVIOUS YOU GUYS
ARE A COUPLE, ISUZU!
OKAY, SINCE YOU DECIDED
TO BRING IT UP...
HOW'RE THINGS GOING
WITH YOU AND NYANTA?
HUH?!
AREN'T YOU LEARNING MORE ABOUT
COOKING AND CLEANING FROM HIM?
THAT'S MORE LIKE
MARRIAGE TRAINING
THAN ADVENTURER TRAINING!
[NYANTA] SERARA...
I MADE SURE I GOT YOU
A RING WORTH FORTY RAIDS!
I ALSO PREPARED THIS FEAST
FOR OUR RECEPTION!
COME AND BE MY BLUSHING
NEWLYWED BRIDE!
SQUEE!
NO, WE'RE NOT LIKE THAT!
WE'RE NOT LIKE THAT!
WE'RE NOT LIKE THAT AT ALL!
[ISUZU] HEY!
[SERARA] I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU GUYS ARE TALKING ABOUT!
[ISUZU] OH, COME ON, SERARA!
YOU GOTTA LEARN...
YOU WON'T BE ABLE
TO ACT LIKE THAT
WHEN YOU BATHE
WITH CHIEF NYANTA!
[BOTH]
BATHE WITH THE CHIEF?!
I COULD GET
USED TO THIS, SERARA.
(SERARA SQUEALS)
[ISUZU] AND...?
[MINORI]
WHAT?
YOU KNOW I'VE GOTTA ASK,
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH
YOU AND SHIROE?
[MINORI]
EH?! WELL... I, UH...
DON'T REALLY HAVE
ANYTHING TO SAY ABOUT IT.
BET THERE'S LOTS OF COMPETITION
FOR THE VILLAIN IN GLASSES.
[MINORI] HM? HUH?
[SERARA] OH!? TELL US MORE?!
[ISUZU] JUST THINK ABOUT IT!
HE STARTED UP THE ROUND TABLE!
[ISUZU] AND MARIELLE AND
HENRIETTA ARE GORGEOUS.
THEY'RE HANGING AROUND
HIM ALL THE TIME!
AND THEN, THERE'S THAT LEADER
OF THE OLD TEA PARTY, TOO.
OH! AND DON'T FORGET
ABOUT THE NINJA!
WHAT D'YOU THINK
YOU'RE LOOKING AT?
YOU WANT HIM YOU GOTTA
GO THROUGH ME!
(DISAPPOINTED BUBBLE BLOWING)
OH AND WHAT ABOUT ROE2, THE TWO
OF THEM MIGHT HAVE A THING, TOO.
[ROE2] HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
THAT'S "BIG SIS," RIGHT?
[ALL] WHA...? HUH?
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
YOU'D DO WELL TO KNOW YOUR BIG
SISTER HAS ADVANTAGES OVER YOU.
AND BY THAT... I MEAN THESE!
[ALL] EH... HUH?!
NO! DON'T EVEN WORRY YOU GUYS!
THOSE THINGS ARE
ONLY FOR SHOW, OKAY?!
[ROE2] HUH? I DIDN'T INTIMIDATE
MY LITTLE SISTERS, NOW, DID I?
(ANNOYED)
MARIELLE? YOU LOOK VERY
SERIOUS, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'VE BEEN THINKING.
I THINK WE SHOULD DO
A SPRING FESTIVAL.
A CHERRY BLOSSOM FESTIVAL
WOULD MAKE MORE SENSE.
HUH... CHERRY...?
SURE THING...
YEAH, RIGHT...
WELL OKAY, THEN...
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD IDEA.
I SUPPOSE...
THAT MIGHT JUST BE THE THING TO
GET EVERYONE HAPPY AGAIN, RIGHT?
OH, MARIELLE...
I REALLY DON'T KNOW IF
THESE FESTIVALS OF OURS
ARE DOING WHAT I'D HOPED...
DO THEY REALLY BRING
PEOPLE TOGETHER?
[NYANTA] WELL, THE SITUATION
IS WHAT IT IS,
BUT IT HASN'T BECOME
A PROBLEM YET, MPH.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
I GET IT,
DO WHAT YOU CAN TO
STAY ON TOP OF IT FOR NOW.
[NYANTA] OF COURSE I WILL,
MPH... HOWEVER...
MY GUESS IS WHAT WE'RE SEEING
RIGHT NOW IS THE RESULT
OF AN UNDERLYING ISSUE THAT
WE HAVEN'T DISCOVERED YET.
ISN'T THAT THE WAY
IT USUALLY WORKS OUT?
(COMMUNICATOR PINGING)
[SHIROE, VOICE CHAT] AKATSUKI?
HOW'RE THINGS OVER THERE?
[AKATSUKI] FINE.
AT LEAST FOR THE TIME BEING...
I'M NOT SEEING ANYTHING UNUSUAL.
SO HOW'RE THINGS GOING
OVER THERE... OKAY?
[SHIROE]
SO FAR, SO GOOD...
THANKS, REPORT BACK
IF YOU SEE ANYTHING.
[AKATSUKI] WILL DO.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
(ENDING PING)
(EXHALE)
WE HAVE A LONG WAY TO GO,
MASTER SHIROE.
IT'S TOO EARLY FOR
YOU TO BE WORN OUT!
WE'VE STILL GOT A LOT OF THINGS
WE NEED TO GET DONE, OKAY?
[SHIROE]
YEAH, YEAH...
[EINS] THE ECONOMIC
DISPARITY IN AKIHABARA
IS CURRENTLY GROWING WORSE
AT AN ALARMING RATE.
PEOPLE WHO CAN HUNT OR DEVELOP
NEW SKILLS ARE GETTING RICHER,
WHILE PLAYERS WHO DIDN'T
HAVE THE RIGHT SKILLS
AT THE TIME OF THE APOCALYPSE
ARE FALTERING IN
MINIMUM WAGE JOBS!
COME ON... WHY ARE YOU
BRINGING THAT UP?!
SO? WHAT DO YOU THINK IS CAUSING
ALL THIS ECONOMIC DISPARITY?
MASTERING ORAL ARTS,
AND CRAFTING CLASSES BEING ABLE
TO CREATE CONSUMER PRODUCTS.
WHAT...? HOW ARE ORAL ARTS
PART OF THE PROBLEM?
ANYONE CAN MASTER ONE
IF THEY REALLY TRY!
OKAY, MAYBE I WASN'T
BEING THAT CLEAR.
LARGER GUILDS HAVE BEEN
USING PEOPLE WITH ORAL ARTS
TO EXPAND BUSINESSES.
ONE OF OUR RESPONSIBILITIES
SHOULD BE TO CURTAIL
THESE MONOPOLIES.
[MICHITAKA] OKAY, YOU'RE
STARTING TO CROSS THE LINE HERE.
[RODERICK] BASED ON SIZE ALONE,
WE COULD ALL ACCUSE YOUR
GUILD OF THE SAME THING, EINS.
[EINS] EXCUSE ME...
FIRST OF ALL, NO ONE IN MY GUILD
HAS MASTERED AN ORAL ART YET!
SECOND, WE SHOULD ALL
HAVE DECLARATIONS FROM
EVERY GUILD WHO ARE USING
PLAYERS WITH ORAL ARTS.
CRAFTING RECIPES SHOULD ALSO...
HEY, WAIT! COME ON, EINS!
YOU KNOW BETTER THAN THAT!
SERIOUSLY, EINS...
YOU CAN'T GO SIMPLY ASKING
PEOPLE TO GIVE AWAY
THEIR CRAFTING SECRETS
JUST LIKE THAT.
SOME OF THESE THINGS
TOOK A WHILE...
FROM RAMEN TO SOAP TO CANDLES...
ALL THOSE CRAFTSMEN
PUT IN A LOT OF TIME
TO MAKE ALL THOSE
THINGS WORK!
AND REMEMBER, DECLARING
ORAL ART USERS IS WORTHLESS,
ONLY THE PERSON WHO MASTERED IT
CAN USE IT. WHAT'S THE POINT?
[EINS] YOU THINK SO? ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT LEVYING A TAX ON
ADVENTURER BANK ACCOUNTS
IN EXCESS OF EIGHTY THOUSAND
GOLD PIECES?
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO
CLOSE THE HUGE GAP
BETWEEN THE RICH AND
THE POOR THAT WAY...
SERIOUSLY, IT'S A PLACE
TO START, I THINK.
YOU'VE LOST YOUR MIND!
UH?!
MAYBE YOU'RE NOT UNDERSTANDING
WHAT WE'VE SAID!
EVERYONE IN THIS CITY HAS
WORKED THEIR BUTTS OFF
TO GET WHERE THEY ARE...!
WE'VE FOUGHT FOR EVERY
LITTLE THING WE'VE GOT.
MAYBE YOU DON'T GET THAT.
[EINS] AND YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND THAT OUR SOCIETY
IS FAVORING CERTAIN
PEOPLE OVER OTHERS.
THE RICH STAY RICH,
AND THE POOR STARVE.
[MARIELLE]
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE EVENTS...
WE'RE MAKING AN EFFORT TO
DO THINGS THAT INCLUDE EVERYONE
FROM ALL LEVELS
AND WALKS OF LIFE.
LISTEN TO YOURSELF,
YOU'RE PUSHING THE
DISENFRANCHISED AWAY!
WATCH IT!
NOW, WAIT...
WE DON'T HOLD THESE FESTIVALS
TO FLAUNT OUR OWN WEALTH!
I JUST WANT EVERYONE
TO BE... Y'KNOW...
SO YOU'RE SAYIN'...
WE GIVE THESE PEOPLE MONEY
AND THEN THEY'LL JUST
GO HAPPILY OFF TO WORK?
MAYBE SO, MAYBE NOT...
BUT WE CAN'T JUST LET THINGS
STAY LIKE THEY ARE.
[KARASHIN] YEAH, BUT IF
YOU'RE GONNA FORCE PEOPLE
TO GIVE UP THEIR NEW RECIPES,
CRAFTSMEN WON'T BE
MOTIVATED TO WORK AS HARD.
[MICHITAKA]
NO MATTER WHAT IT'S FOR,
ALL OF THOSE RECIPES TAKE
A LOT OF WORK TO CREATE!
[SHIROE, THINKING] WHAT I WOULD
GIVE TO HAVE KRUSTY HERE NOW...
[EINS]
YOU'RE MISSING THE POINT HERE...
[MICHITAKA] YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT!
(CLAPPING)
[ALL] HM?
[SHIROE] I UNDERSTAND THE
GIST OF YOUR PROPOSAL...
AND IT MAKES SENSE
THAT WE NEED SOME KIND OF
POLICY TO HANDLE THIS.
HOWEVER, THE ROUND TABLE HAS
A LIMITED BUDGET
FOR THIS KIND OF THING.
UNLIKE MINAMI,
WE DON'T GET OPERATING FUNDS
FROM AN ARISTOCRACY.
[SHIROE]
WE ALL NEED TO TAKE A ROLE
IN DETERMINING HOW WE
CAN HANDLE THIS PROBLEM.
ALL RIGHT... BUT WE CAN'T WAIT
UNTIL IT'S OUT OF CONTROL.
[SHIROE] AND WE CAN'T BE
HASTY ABOUT THIS!
LOOK A DECISION OF THIS SCALE
COULD WRECK OUR ECONOMY
IF WE DON'T DO IT RIGHT!
AND WE WOULD END UP
LEAVING THE CITY IN CHAOS!
[TOYA]
HMMM...
I KNOW WE WOULDN'T EVEN BE
IN THE BOXROOT MOUNTAINS
IF IT WEREN'T FOR
BIG SIS ROE2'S HORSES...
BUT THIS ROAD IS A NIGHTMARE!
[MINORI]
YEAH, BACK IN THE REAL WORLD
THIS WOULD BE
RIGHT AROUND HAKONE.
[MINORI] IT WAS A VOLCANO,
SO THIS MAKES SENSE.
WHATEVER YOU SAY...
SO DO WE GO ON AHEAD?
THE VISIBILITY'S
REALLY LOUSY OUT THERE!
UH‐HUH.
[TOYA]
UGH. SULFUR...
[RUDY]
HANG ON. I SHALL ACCOMPANY YOU.
[ROE2] ALLOW ME TO SUMMON
SOME COMPANIONS FOR YOU!
I MEAN AFTER ALL,
I AM YOUR BIG SIS!
[TOYA]
COMPANIONS?
(SURPRISED)
[RUDY]
I DON'T THINK SO!
[TOYA]
NO THANKS! I'LL PASS.
[SERARA]
HANG ON... TAKE WOLFY WITH YOU!
[WOLFY]
YIP‐YIP‐YIP!
[TOYA] THANKS YOU GUYS!
THIS OUGHTA WORK.
(YIPS AND BARKS)
[RUDY] WELL I GUESS WE CAN GO!
[TOYA, NASALLY] GEEZ! I SWEAR
THIS SULFUR SMELL IS RANK!
[RUDY]
I WARNED YOU GUYS ABOUT THIS...
BOXROOT IS NOT AN EASY PASSAGE.
I HAVE TO SAY, THOUGH,
THE HAZE IS MUCH THICKER
THAN THE LAST TIME I WAS HERE.
[WOLFY] YIP‐YIP‐YIP!
[TOYA] HUH?
[RUDY] LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE HAVING PROBLEMS.
[MAN B] WE'VE STILL GOT
A LOT LEFT HERE...
[RUDY] YOU NEED SOME HELP?
[ALL] HUH? HMM...
[MAN A] PLEASE TELL ME YOU'RE
ADVENTURERS! YOU NEED A SWORD?
GOT A BUNCH OF LEVELS,
TEN TO FIFTEEN!
SOME OF AKIHABARA'S FINEST!
[TOYA] NOT REALLY...! OUR LEVELS
ARE TOO HIGH FOR THAT STUFF!
[TOYA]
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU GUYS?
[MAN B] WELL, Y'SEE,
OUR CART BROKE DOWN.
[RUDY]
WELL IF THAT'S THE CASE,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST PUT WHAT
YOU CAN IN THE OTHER CART?
AND THEN JUST SHOVE THE BROKEN
CART OFF THE MOUNTAINSIDE!
[WOMAN A] WE CAN'T JUST
THROW OUR CARGO AWAY!
[MAN A] COME ON! BE A SPORT
AND BUY A COUPLE OFF OF US!
[MAN B] WE'D REALLY
APPRECIATE IT!
[WOMAN A] I BET BOTH OF
YOU HAVE ENOUGH GOLD!
NO, WE REALLY DON'T!
I'D LOVE TO BUY SOME,
BUT I CAN'T.
[DARIELLA] PLEASE DON'T THINK
POORLY OF THEM, DEAR TRAVELERS.
[BOTH] HUH?
THE AXLE GAVE WAY
AND WE'RE STUCK.
I'M AFRAID WE'VE BEEN TRAPPED
HERE FOR AN ENTIRE DAY.
PLEASE PARDON THEIR MANNERS.
HUH...? UH... WHO'RE YOU?
MY NAME IS DARIELLA...
I AM BUT A HUMBLE PERSON OF
THE LAND AND A CHRONICLER.
IT'S A PLEASURE, MILADY.
I AM RUNDELLHAUS KODE
AND THIS IS TOYA.
ADVENTURERS FROM AKIHABARA.
[DARIELLA]
REALLY! YOU'RE FROM AKIHABARA?
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD CARRY
SOME OF THE CRATES
TO THE NEXT SETTLEMENT?
I KNOW HOW STRONG YOU
ADVENTURERS HAPPEN TO BE...
AND I'M SURE THE MERCHANTS
WOULD APPRECIATE IT!
[TOYA]
UH...
[MAN A]
OH, WOW!
YOU'RE AWFULLY STRONG
FOR SUCH A SCRAWNY LASS,
MISS... UH, IZUMAMI!
[ISUZU]
MY NAME'S ISUZU!
[MINORI]
EXCUSE ME,
THERE DOESN'T SEEM TO
BE ANYTHING IN THESE BOXES
BUT A BUNCH OF GOAT SLIMES!
[WOMAN A] YEAH, SOME WEIRD
OLD FART IN AKIHABARA
DUMPED THEM ON US.
NOT SURE WHAT THE DEAL WAS.
(SNORING)
[TOYA] (LAUGH) THAT'S FUNNY!
THEY ATE ALL THE FOOD
AND PASSED RIGHT OUT!
[DARIELLA] WE SPENT THE NIGHT
ON A MOUNTAIN ROAD,
COMPLETELY EXPOSED.
IT'S NO WONDER
THEY'RE EXHAUSTED.
IT WAS A DIFFICULT NIGHT.
[TOYA] OH...
[MINORI] YOU'RE NOT MARRIED
TO ONE OF THE MERCHANTS
ARE YOU MISS DARIELLA?
OH NOTHING LIKE THAT...
THEY WERE JUST LETTING ME
RIDE WITH THEM
THE REST OF THE WAY TO MINAMI.
[TOYA]
OH, UH... HUH?
[ROE2] ISN'T MINAMI IN THE
SAME DIRECTION AS IKOMA?
[DARIELLA] IT IS.
[SERARA] HEY EVERYBODY!
WE'RE GONNA HAVE SOME TEA
HERE READY IN A MINUTE!
WE'VE GOT PASTRIES!
[ROE2] MMMM! I LOVE YOU.
(SERARA GIGGLING)
[SERARA] THESE COOKIES
WERE MADE BY NONE OTHER
THAN OUR OWN CHIEF NYANTA!
[ALL] OHHH!
[RUDY] YOU'RE GONNA LOVE 'EM!
[MINORI]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
[ISUZU]
THEY'RE GREAT!
[DARIELLA]
IT'S SWEET. I LIKE IT!
(TOYA MUNCHING)
(MUNCH) SO WHERE IS
IT YOU'RE ALL GOING?
[MINORI] WE'RE HEADED TO
THE REDSTONE MOUNTAINS.
I'M HEADED TO IKOMA, NOW...
BUT I PLAN ON STICKING
WITH THEM TILL I GET THERE.
THEY'D NEED ME TO PROTECT THEM!
[DARIELLA] OH REALLY...?
I GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE...
YOU ALL DO LOOK KIND OF YOUNG.
[RUDY] ONCE WE GET OVER THE
PASS WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
(SNOOZING)
[MINORI] YEAH...
BUT MASTER SHIROE SAID WE COULD
END UP RUNNING INTO WYVERNS
IN THE MOUNTAINS AROUND HERE.
HUH?
[ISUZU] AREN'T WYVERNS SUPPOSED
TO BE AN AERIAL‐TYPE MONSTER?
[SERARA] MAYBE THEY FOUND SOME
NEW PLACES THEY COULD CALL HOME.
[MINORI] THE GROUNDLING
MONSTERS ARE DOING THAT...
SO I GUESS IT'S POSSIBLE.
[DARIELLA]
MM‐HM.
(OMINOUS ECHOING)
[ISUZU] WHAT WAS THAT?
[SERARA] IT SORTA SOUNDS LIKE
CHURCH BELLS AT A FUNERAL.
[MINORI]
THEY'RE COMING THIS WAY!
[SERARA]
ARE THEY A RAID PARTY...?
[MINORI]
LET'S SEE... JUST A SEC...
THEY'RE WITH PLANT HWYADEN!
[ISUZU]
FROM MINAMI?!
[TOYA]
THAT GUY'S A LEVEL 90.
[SERARA] EVERYBODY ELSE
IN THE PARTY IS, TOO!
[ISUZU]
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THEY'RE
A GROUP OF PLAYER KILLERS.
[DARIELLA] IT'S POSSIBLE...
THEY MIGHT BE
THE ODYSSEY KNIGHTS.
[TOYA] AS IN THE GUYS WHO
PROTECT NPCS? THOSE KNIGHTS?
[MINORI]
MM‐HM.
[ROE2] WHAT'S THAT THING
THEY'RE CARRYING?
I'VE NEVER SEEN ONE BEFORE.
[DARIELLA] IT'S THE
PORTABLE SHRINE OF BOREAS.
[ROE2]
A PORTABLE SHRINE?!
[DARIELLA] I LEARNED ABOUT
THIS DURING MY TRAVELS.
THE ODYSSEY KNIGHTS TAKE
THE SHRINE WITH THEM
ON THEIR JOURNEYS
ACROSS THE LANDSCAPE.
IT HAS THE POWER TO
REVIVE ANY ADVENTURER
AS LONG AS THEY'RE
CLOSE ENOUGH TO IT.
INSTANT RESURRECTION.
NO TIME DELAY OTHER THAN WAITING
FOR YOUR MANA TO REASSEMBLE.
IT'S LIKE HAVING
YOUR OWN CATHEDRAL.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE THE
ADVENTURERS IN MINAMI
CREATED THAT DEVICE?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THEM?
THEY SEEM SO LIFELESS...
[RUDY] IT'S ALMOST LIKE
A FUNERAL MARCH.
[DARIELLA]
I'M NOT SURE ABOUT THIS...
BUT INSTANT REBIRTH
CARRIES A PRICE WITH IT...
IT SUPPOSEDLY UPSETS THE VOICE
OF THE MIND IN ADVENTURERS.
UPSETS THE VOICE OF THE MIND?
[DARIELLA]
I SUPPOSE SOMETHING LIKE THAT
WOULD BE EXTREMELY VALUABLE TO
ADVENTURERS SUCH AS YOURSELVES.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
UH...!
[TOYA]
OHH... UH?
(HALF‐GIGGLE)
(BREATH)
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
THE JUNIOR MEMBERS VISIT
SAPHIR VILLAGE ON THEIR JOURNEY.
ISUZU THE BARD TREATS
THE VILLAGE TO A SHOW.
HER MELODY HEARTILY ENCHANTS
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
WHILE HAPPINESS
AND A PLEASANT FEELING
OF EXHAUSTION ENVELOP ISUZU,
RUNDELLHAUS TELLS HER
OF A SECRET
BEHIND THIS WORLD'S MUSIC.
HE SHARES THE DREAMS OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND!
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.