[GUY A] ANOTHER MURDER? HE'S
LIKE SOME SORT OF SERIAL KILLER!
[GUY B] WHY DOES HE EVEN DO IT?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE
REALLY DIE ANYWAY.
[GIRL A] I KNOW!
THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT SO CRAZY!
SO HOW MANY PEOPLE
HAS HE KILLED?
NO IDEA HOW MANY HE'S UP TO,
BUT DURING CHRISTMAS?
YEAH, TELL ME ABOUT IT, MAN.
WE WERE HAVING A HARD ENOUGH
TIME SELLING THINGS.
SO THEN, WHY HAVEN'T THE ROYAL
GUARDS DONE ANYTHING ABOUT IT?
HMMM, I DUNNO.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
THE ROYAL GUARDS
ARE THIS WORLD'S
PEACEKEEPING FORCE,
DATING BACK TO WHEN WE WERE
PLAYING ELDER TALES AS A GAME.
IF SOMEONE TRIES TO FIGHT OR PK
IN A NON PLAYER‐VERSUS‐PLAYER
ZONE, THEY APPEAR IMMEDIATELY
AND STOP THE FIGHTING.
EVEN THOUGH THERE ARE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND INSIDE THE
MOVEABLE ARMOR SUITS, OUTSIDE
MAGIC GIVES THEM THEIR POWER.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS THE ROYAL
GUARD WILL ALWAYS BE ABLE
TO SUBDUE AN ADVENTURER
OF ANY CLASS,
NO MATTER HOW POWERFUL
THAT ADVENTURER IS,
NO MATTER WHAT
LEVEL THEIR ITEMS.
THIS IS HOW THEY MAINTAIN ORDER.
[HARUHARU] WELL, IT'S THE
NIGHT BEFORE CHRISTMAS EVE.
[YOSHISUKE]
AND WE'RE STUCK OUT HERE!
[COOL JET]
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
[TOSHI] NOTHING UNUSUAL SO FAR.
LET'S CHECK THE NEXT BLOCK.
[HARUHARU]
IT'S HARD TO FIND SOMETHING
WHEN YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
[YOSHISUKE]
YEAH, IT'S NOT EVEN A QUEST.
[COOL JET] AW MAN!
IT IS REALLY COLD OUT HERE.
[YOSHISUKE] HEY!
[COOL JET] IT'S HIM!
[HARUHARU]
WHEN DID HE GET THERE?!
[TOSHI] STATUS! WE GOTTA
FIGURE OUT WHO HE IS AND QUICK!
[NERURESU] HUNNNHHH!
HE'S COMING PRETTY FAST!
HE'S ON US!
(LAUGHING)
[MICHITAKA]
WIPED THEM ALL OUT?
THAT'S RIGHT. AND THEY WERE
ALL EXPERIENCED PLAYERS.
HE SLICED HIS WAY THROUGH
THEM LIKE IT WAS NOTHING.
[SOJIRO]
THIS GUY'S FORCED THE RE‐SPAWN
OF AT LEAST TEN ADVENTURERS.
[MARIELLE] WE LEARNED HIS NAME
IS ENBART NERURESU.
HE'S NOT IN A GUILD.
IT SAYS HE'S A SAMURAI,
AND HE'S A LEVEL 94.
THAT'S ALL THE INFORMATION
WE COULD DIG UP ON HIM.
[WOODSTOCK] OKAY THEN,
WE CAN'T JUST SIT AROUND,
NOT IF WE ALREADY KNOW
WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT THE GUY.
HMM... SO THEN THIS
KNUCKLEHEAD IS RUNNING AROUND
KILLING ADVENTURERS FOR KICKS,
BIG DEAL,
WE DON'T DIE.
I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE NOT WORRIED,
BUT WE CAN'T JUST LET
HIM KEEP DOING THIS.
IT'S TRUE. OUR VERY
WAY OF LIFE IS IN DANGER,
THE PEACE WE HAVE ENJOYED
IS CRUMBLING AWAY.
AND SO, I BELIEVE
WE SHOULD CONSIDER
AN EVACUATION OF THE CITY.
[MICHITAKA] YOU WANT US
TO ABANDON AKIHABARA?!
[EINS] WE NEED TO TAKE
EMERGENCY MEASURES!
FOR INSTANCE,
WE COULD MOVE TO SHIBUYA.
THAT'S A LITTLE BIT MUCH!
AND BESIDES, WE SHOULDN'T BE
MAKING A DECISION LIKE THAT
FOR EVERYONE ELSE
LIVING IN THE CITY.
HMMM....
[MARIELLE]
MAYBE NOT,
BUT SHOULDN'T WE START GATHERING
UP ALL THE LOWER LEVEL KIDS
AND GETTING THEM OUT OF HERE?
NOW THAT MIGHT BE AN
IDEA WORTH LOOKING AT.
THIS IS CRAZY,
I CAN'T BELIEVE SOMETHING
LIKE THIS IS EVEN HAPPENING...
[MICHITAKA]
WE'VE GOTTA FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO SHUT THIS GUY DOWN FOR GOOD.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
BY THE WAY, WHAT'S THE VILLAIN
IN GLASSES UP TO, RIGHT NOW?
THE FOUNDER OF THE ROUND TABLE
SHOULD BE HERE, SHOULDN'T HE?
UH, WELL IT'S...
KINDA LIKE THIS.
I'VE HEARD HE'S BEEN BUSY
TRYING TO RAISE MONEY.
PLUS, WE ALL KNOW DECEMBER IS A
HECTIC MONTH WITH THE HOLIDAYS!
AND WE HAVE BIG PLANS
FOR TOMORROW'S EVENT!
WHY ZANTLEAF?
WELL, MY MAN.
THERE'S A REQUEST
FOR ANYONE OUT THERE
UNDER LEVEL FIFTY TO FINISH
HUNTING DOWN THE GOBLINS.
IT'S A GOOD WAY TO KEEP
LEVELING YOURSELF UP.
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE AN EXCUSE
TO GET US OUT OF THE CITY
WHILE THEY HUNT DOWN THE KILLER.
[NYANTA] WELL, YES,
THAT MIGHT ACTUALLY BE
A NICE SIDE EFFECT, MYAH.
OH COME ON! I WANNA PIECE OF
THE ACTION TOO! WE CAN FIGHT!
TOYA!
SO, YOU WANT TO BE THE ONE
TO SLAY THE SERIAL KILLER?
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT, CHIEF!
JUST ONE MISTAKE
CAN GET YOU KILLED.
SURE, I KNOW THAT CAN HAPPEN.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW YOU'RE ALWAYS
GOING TO COME BACK TO LIFE?
NO, I GUESS, I DIDN'T
MEAN IT THAT WAY.
YEAH, LITTLE MAN.
WHAT I MEANT...
[NYANTA] IF YOU'RE A
FIGHTER ON THE FRONT LINE,
YOU SHOULDN'T BE
SO EAGER TO DIE, MYAH.
I... OH. I GET IT.
I'D ONLY END UP BREAKING
THE FORMATION, WOULDN'T I?
AND THAT'S NOT GOOD.
[NYANTA] YES, BUT THAT'S
NOT THE ONLY REASON.
RESURRECTION IS QUITE A GIFT.
IT'S A SPECIAL TREATMENT
GIVEN TO US
JUST BECAUSE
WE PLAYED A VIDEO GAME.
IF WE TAKE IT FOR GRANTED
AND GET ACCUSTOMED TO
BEING ABLE TO CHEAT DEATH.
WE MIGHT END UP
LOSING SOMETHING
MORE PRECIOUS TO US
IN THE PROCESS,
Y'KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
[MINORI, THINKING]
MISS AKATSUKI NEVER MADE IT
BACK TO THE HOUSE TODAY.
[DISTANT VOICE]
IT'S CHRISTMAS EVE!
WHY DON'T WE GO OUT TO EAT?
MY TREAT, GUYS.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
WHERE ARE YOU...
WHERE ARE YOU...?
[DISTANT VOICE] THIS WHOLE
SERIAL KILLER THING IS CRAZY!
[DISTANT VOICE] I KNOW.
(DISTANT GIGGLING)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
TOO MUCH INTERFERENCE.
I JUST WISH I COULD GET FOCUSED.
WOULD MY LORD BE ANGRY
IF HE KNEW I WAS UP TO
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
[SHIROE]
KEEP HER SAFE, AKATSUKI.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] WHAT DOES
HE WANT ME TO PROTECT HER FROM?
I KNOW THAT THE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND ARE WEAKER THAN WE ARE...
BUT I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT OF
HER AS BEING PRETTY STRONG.
I MEAN, MORE THAN MOST.
DO I HAVE ANY NEED
TO PROTECT HER?
AM I EVEN THAT MUCH
STRONGER THAN SHE IS?
DO I HAVE RIGHT TO ASK THAT?
I MUST GET STRONGER.
[SOJIRO] OUR ENEMY IS
EXTREMELY TOUGH, EVERYONE.
NO MATTER HOW GOOD
YOU'VE BEEN IN A RAID BEFORE,
WE CAN'T LET HIM
CATCH US OFF‐GUARD.
YOU MUST CONSIDER THIS ADVERSARY
TO BE STRONGER THAN
ANYONE YOU'VE EVER FACED.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE ALONE,
AND STAY IN CONTACT.
COMMUNICATION IS KEY.
YOU'RE UP NAZNA...
DON'T PLAY THE HERO OUT THERE.
BE SURE TO USE FORMATION ALPHA
IF YOU FIND YOURSELF
IN A FIGHT WITH THE
SUBJECT, OKAY GUYS?
NOW THERE'S ONE OTHER THING,
EACH TEAM WILL HAVE TWO
HEALERS FOR RECUPERATION.
REMEMBER ITS CONNAISSANCE...
BUY TIME, KEEP US POSTED,
AND DON'T GET YOURSELF KILLED.
GOT IT?
[ALL]
ROGER!
ALL RIGHT, YOU HAVE
ANYTHING TO ADD?
[SOJIRO] (SIGH)
WELL, YOU KNOW.
I THINK YOU'VE SAID EVERYTHING
I WANTED TO SAY ALREADY.
WELL, THERE IS ONE THING...
THIS BASTARD PKED
A MEMBER OF OUR FAMILY!
TAKE HIM OUT.
OHH... THIS IS GREAT!
THIS IS SO AWESOME!
YEAH!
(CHATTER)
COME ON, NAZNA!
DON'T YOU THINK I SHOULD BE OKAY
TO GO OUT ON PATROL BY NOW?
I WANT THE FIRST SHOT
AT REVENGE ON THIS GUY!
EAH, WELL, YOU JUST TOOK
ANOTHER TRIP TO THE CATHEDRAL;
YOU'RE STILL GONNA NEED
A COUPLE DAYS.
IT'S JUST TOUGH SEEING
MASTER SOJIRO AND EVERYONE
DEFENDING ME LIKE THIS.
IT'S NOTHING YOU SHOULD
TAKE PERSONALLY, YOU KNOW?
IF ANYONE IN OUR GUILD
GETS PKED,
SOJI WILL MAKE SURE HE PAYS.
(SLURPING) 'CAUSE
THAT'S THE WAY HE IS.
YEAH, I KNOW HE IS.
MASTER SOJIRO DOES WHAT HE CAN
TO KEEP US FROM GETTING HURT.
(SIPS)
BUT STILL, I CAN DREAM OF
TAKING MY REVENGE, CAN'T I?
[NAZNA] (GIGGLE)
NEVER SEEN THIS BEFORE!
WHOEVER HEARD OF PORK MISO SOUP
ON CHRISTMAS EVE?
[KYOKO] YEAH! AND THIS ONE
HAS SALMON IN IT!
[NAZNA, THINKING] MASTER SOJIRO
IS KIND TO US, IT'S TRUE.
BUT I GET THE FEELING,
IT'S NOT BECAUSE HE HAS
SOME HEART OF GOLD,
IT'S JUST HIS NATURE...
HE LOOKS CALM, BUT I KNOW
HE'S LOST HIS PATIENCE.
THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT HE'LL
DO NEXT.
WHAT'S THE OLD SAYING, "NEVER
MISTAKE KINDNESS FOR WEAKNESS?"
(PING)
[SOJIRO] UH? OH!
[NAZNA, THINKING] IF ONLY
KAZUHIKO AND SHIROE WERE HERE.
THEY'RE THE ONLY TWO
THAT CAN MAKE SOJIRO
CHANGE HIS MIND
WHEN HE'S THIS DETERMINED.
[NAOTSUGU]
I KNOW, I'M REALLY SORRY!
YEAH, THAT MIGHT BE A BETTER
DAY, LET'S SHOOT FOR NEW YEARS.
REALLY?
SO YOU'RE SAYING YOU HAVEN'T
FOUND THE SERIAL KILLER YET?
I TAKE IT YOU'VE BEEN
DOING ROUNDS.
YEAH, UH, YOU KNOW YOU DON'T
NEED TO WORRY ABOUT US.
[SOJIRO, VOICEOVER] AND WELL!
AKATSUKI'S BEEN WORKING HARD.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
OF COURSE, AND YOU TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF, SHIROE!
SOJI!
HMPH... WE FINALLY SPOTTED HIM.
(CRYING OUT)
[NAZNA] I TOLD THE INVESTIGATION
TEAM TO GET OUT OF THERE.
LET'S FIND HIM, SURROUND HIM,
AND KILL HIM!
[KINJO] I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU IN
SOME TIME, PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] THIS IS
LORD KINJO OF THE KUNIE TRIBE,
I WONDER WHAT BRINGS HIM HERE
WITHOUT EVEN CALLING ON ME.
[KINJO]
IT APPEARS I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
FIRST BECAUSE I GAVE YOU NO
PRIOR NOTICE OF THIS VISIT.
HOWEVER THE SECOND INVOLVES
A MATTER OF SOME GRAVITY
TO THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
YOU'RE FORGIVEN FOR THE FIRST,
WHAT'S THE SECOND?
I TAKE IT YOU'RE FAMILIAR
WITH THE MOVABLE ARMOR?
ADVENTURERS KNOW THEM
DIFFERENTLY,
THEY TEND TO REFER TO THEM
COLLECTIVELY AS THE ROYAL GUARD.
YES, NATURALLY,
I'M AWARE OF THEIR ROLE
IN KEEPING THE PEACE.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
A SET OF MOVABLE ARMOR
HAS BEEN STOLEN FROM
THE PALATIAL GUARDROOM.
WHAT?
[KINJO] A MEMBER OF THE
ROYAL GUARD HAS TAKEN IT.
I ALSO BELIEVE HE HAPPENS TO
BE A MEMBER OF THE KUNIE TRIBE.
(GASP)
[KINJO] A GIANT MAGIC CIRCLE
UNDER THE CITY
CONSTANTLY SUPPLIES A GUARD'S
MOVABLE ARMOR WITH POWER.
THE CONSTRUCTION OF THE MAGIC
CIRCLE VARIES WITH EACH CITY.
GEOGRAPHY AND THE PLACEMENT
OF BUILDING ALL ARE FACTORS.
SO IF I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TELLING ME,
HE WON'T BE ABLE TO
LEAVE THE CITY WITH IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
HE'S NEARLY INVINCIBLE
WITHIN THE CITY.
AND THE AMOUNT OF MAGIC
HE CAN DRAW
MAKES HIM FAR STRONGER
THAN ANY ADVENTURER.
(GASP)
SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING EXACTLY?
I AM SAYING THAT MY TRIBE...
MAY BE RESPONSIBLE
FOR ALL THE MURDERS.
IT SHAMES ME, BUT I CANNOT
DENY THE POSSIBILITY.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
IN OTHER WORDS,
A PERSON OF THE LAND
IS KILLING ADVENTURERS.
OUR NEGLIGENCE ALLOWED THIS
TO HAPPEN, YOUR MAJESTY.
YOU HAVE MY SINCEREST APOLOGIES.
(EXHALE)
WELL THEN,
CAN THE KUNIE TRIBE DEVISE A
METHOD OF FIXING THIS?
FIND A WAY OF MAKING THIS RIGHT?
FOR THAT I APOLOGIZE AS WELL.
I DON'T THINK WE CAN.
HOWEVER, WE CAN DEPRIVE
THE ARMOR OF ITS POWER
BY SHUTTING OFF THE MAGIC
TO THE CITY'S CIRCLE.
OF COURSE, THIS WOULD ALSO
NEUTRALIZE THE CITY'S
OTHER MAGICAL DEFENSES.
THERE WOULD BE NOTHING STOPPING
MONSTERS FROM COMING IN.
WELL, IF YOU
WERE TO TRY THIS,
COULDN'T YOU JUST
RESTORE THE CIRCLE
RIGHT AFTER HE'S ELIMINATED?
I'M AFRAID IT'S NOT
THAT SIMPLE, YOUR GRACE.
IT WOULD TAKE
DECADES TO RESTORE.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] THIS IS ONE
TIME, I WISH I DIDN'T EAVESDROP.
BUT I HEARD ALL OF THAT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER,
WHAT CAN I DO ABOUT IT?
I NEED YOU TO PROTECT THE
PRINCESS WHILE I'M GONE.
[RAYNESHIA]
GREAT! THAT'S IT THEN!
THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT THIS!
WHY IN THE WORLD DID
IT HAVE TO HAPPEN NOW?!
AND WHY DID IT HAVE TO
BE ME OF ALL PEOPLE?
IT'S NOT LIKE I KNOW HOW
TO SOLVE SOMETHING
THAT'S SO BIG AND
OUT OF CONTROL!
WHY DID IT HAVE TO HAPPEN
WHILE I WAS WORKING HERE?!
I NEED SOMEONE ELSE TO
SHOW ME A WAY OUT OF THIS!
PLEASE JUST SOMEBODY HELP ME.
WHAT IN THE WORLD
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
WHY DON'T YOU ASK THE
ROUND TABLE FOR HELP?
[RAYNESHIA] SERIOUSLY,
IF I TELL THEM WHAT'S GOING ON,
IT WON'T DO ANYTHING
EXCEPT CREATE A WAR
WITH ALL OF THE ADVENTURERS!
POSSIBLY, BUT KEEPING
QUIET DOES NOTHING.
[RAYNESHIA] OKAY, FINE.
YOU REALLY THINK I SHOULD
JUST TELL THEM?
[AKATSUKI] IT'S NOT MY PLACE
TO TELL YOU EITHER WAY.
[RAYNESHIA] WHY ISN'T THAT
IGNORANT FOUR‐EYED MONSTER
HERE WHEN I NEED HIM MOST?!
HE WAS ALWAYS STICKING
HIS NOSE IN MY BUSINESS
WHEN I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO.
HE'S NOT GOING TO BE HERE,
HE'S ON HIS WAY TO SEVENTH FALL.
[RAYNESHIA] YES, I KNOW HE IS...
BUT THAT'S NO EXCUSE.
UGH, WAS THAT OUTLOUD? UGH...
NNNGH
(EXHALE)
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT, OKAY?!
AHH!
[AKATSUKI]
HUH?
[RAYNESHIA]
UUHHH...
[AKATSUKI]
HUH?
SO... I GUESS...
I'M SORRY. I WENT AHEAD
AND LET MYSELF IN.
OKAY, YOU HEARD ALL THAT.
I DID.
OF COURSE YOU DID.
(PAPER CRINKLING)
UH...
YOU WANT ONE?
IT'S SWEET. I LIKE IT.
(MUFFLED) UH‐HUH. SWEETS ARE
GOOD IN TIMES LIKE THIS.
YES, I SUPPOSE THAT'S BECAUSE
THE WORLD ISN'T KIND OR SWEET.
UH... NO, NOT RIGHT NOW.
[AKATSUKI]
SO HE'S AN NPC?
[RAYNESHIA]
YES, HE IS.
I AM REALLY, VERY SORRY
ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
OKAY THEN...
HUH?
THIS GUY THAT WE'RE AFTER,
YOU KNOW HIS WHEREABOUTS?
WE DON'T KNOW WHERE HE IS,
OR WHY HE DECIDED TO STEAL IT.
I HAVE A FEELING...
HE'S DOWN IN THE SEWERS.
HUH?
IF HE'S GOING TO LOSE HIS
POWERS OUTSIDE THE CITY,
THEN HE'S ONLY GOT A
FEW PLACES TO HIDE
AND THAT'S THE MOST LIKELY.
HE CAN'T BRING A LOT OF
ATTENTION TO HIMSELF,
AND HE NEEDS TO BE EVERYWHERE
AND NOWHERE AT THE SAME TIME.
[RAYNESHIA] SO THEN WE SHOULD
BE ABLE TO CATCH HIM RIGHT AWAY
IF WE GO AFTER HIM?!
NO, THE ROYAL GUARD CAN USE
TELEPORTATION MAGIC.
IF WE SURROUND HIM,
HE CAN DISAPPEAR.
YES, OF COURSE...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
HER SHOULDERS ARE SO SLIM.
I CAN'T IMAGINE HOW HARD IT IS.
TO BE SO DELICATE AND
HAVE SO MUCH RESPONSIBILITY
IT'S JUST AMAZING TO ME.
[AKATSUKI]
IT'S BAD, HUH?
[RAYNESHIA]
YES IT REALLY IT.
[AKATSUKI]
THEN I'LL GET HIM.
[RAYNESHIA]
WHAT?
YOU DO YOUR BEST TO FIND A WAY.
AND I WILL AS WELL.
I PROMISE YOU.
HUH?
[SHIROE] SWITCH TANKS GUYS!
NAOTSUGU, RILE HIM UP!
THAT'S MUSIC TO MY EARS!
HEY, STUPID! I GOT
SOMETHING FOR YOUR ASS!
[KAWARA/ISAMI]
HAAHHHHH!
[NERURESU]
HEHE
[KAWARA/ISAMI]
WAAAUUUGHHH!
(GROANS)
(GRUNT)
(LAUGHTER)
(STRUGGLED EFFORT)
(GROWL)
(GASP)
UH! (GASP)
MASTER SOJIRO!
GET BACK, ISAMI!
C'MON, DON'T FADE ON ME!
WHAT IS THIS?! I DON'T GET IT!
WE LANDED A BUNCH OF HITS ON HIM
AND HE DIDN'T LOSE ANY HP!
[KAWARA] SOMETHING'S WEIRD
WITH HIS STATUS BAR, TOO!
[OLIVE] I KNOW, AND WE'VE
BEEN OUT HERE FIGHTING
FOR A LONG TIME WITH
NO SIGN OF THE ROYAL GUARD!
IF MASTER SOJIRO DIDN'T SHOW UP
WE WOULDN'T HAVE MADE IT.
WE'VE GOTTA HELP HIM OUT!
YOU CAN'T...
THE ALLEY IS TOO NARROW,
ALL YOU'D DO IS GET IN HIS WAY.
[NAZNA]
JUST LET HIM HANDLE THIS.
(GRUNT, LAUGHTER)
[OLIVE]
YEAH, HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
(ROAR)
[NERURESU]
HEHE.
IS HE REALLY A SAMURAI?
HE SEEMS DIFFERENT
THAN MASTER SOJI.
[NAZNA] DIVINE EYE.
[ALL]HUH?
[NAZNA]
IT'S SOJI'S ORAL ART.
IT ALLOWS HIM TO SEE THE PATH
HIS OPPONENT IS
GOING TO USE TO STRIKE.
BUT EVEN WITH IT,
THINGS ARE STILL CLOSE.
HE NORMALLY DODGES
ATTACKS LIKE THAT,
BUT NOW IT'S MAKING HIM BLOCK.
SOJIRO...
(YELLING)
[ISAMI] (GASP) MASTER!
[KAWARA] MASTER!
[OLIVE]
MASTER SOJI!
(GASP)
[NAZNA, THINKING]
HE BROKE THROUGH MY BARRIER.
THAT WAS SUPPOSED
TO HELP HIM
KEEP 20 PERCENT OF
HIS HIT‐POINTS!
HE WON'T LAST VERY LONG
IF THIS KEEPS UP!
HE MIGHT NEED TO FALL BACK,
BUT HE HAS TO BE
VERY CAREFUL ABOUT IT.
OTHERWISE THAT SON OF
A BITCH'LL JUST TURN AROUND
AND START TEARING US TO SHREDS.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE SOJI
CAN HOLD HIM BACK ON HIS OWN.
HWUH, UH, AH!
(DISTANT CHATTERING
AND BABBLING)
[GIRL] ABSOLUTELY WONDERFUL
TIME. AND THERE'S SNOW!
(DISTANT VOICES
OVERLAPPING EACH OTHER)
[GIRL] I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
TO MAKE A SNOW ANGEL
[NAZNA]
LOOK OUT!
[AKATSUKI]
UH?
(GRUNT)
(SLASHING)
UWAHH!
[SOJIRO]
AKATSUKI...
[NAZNA]
THIS CHANGES THINGS.
[AKATSUKI]
ACCELERATOR FANG!
UWAHHH!
GOOD TO SEE YOU,
YOU CARE TO HELP?
STEALTH BLADE!
WAHHH!
YAH!
AH!
[AKATSUKI] RAPID ASSAULT!
(GRUNTS)
THAT GIRL! SHE'S INCREDIBLE!
MMM.
(GRUNT)
GUSTING STEP!
[NERURESU]
RAAHHHHHHH!
EH!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
THAT ATTACK WOULD HAVE KILLED ME
IF SOMEONE HADN'T
CAST A BARRIER.
HE'S STRONG!
AND I'VE SEEN THAT SWORD BEFORE.
RUN FOR IT!
I DON'T THINK SO.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
NGH? WHAT?
WHY SHOULD I?
GETTING A WIN AND SOLVING
THE PROBLEM AREN'T THE SAME.
[SOJIRO]
MM‐HM.
[NERURESU]
HAHHHHHHH!
ASSASSINATION!
(INHALE, LAUGH)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
AT LEAST FOR NOW,
THAT'S THE STRONGEST
ATTACK I HAVE.
[AKATSUKI]
SOJIRO, YOU NEED TO GO!
[SOJIRO] YOU SHOULD KNOW BY NOW
THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN!
(SHARP INHALE)
NAZNA, GET BACK!
ROGER!
WE'LL REGROUP AT THE HALL!
SEE YOU THERE!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] HE WAS
LOOKING OUT FOR HIS GUILD‐MATES?
EVEN WHILE HE WAS FIGHTING?
HE WAS KEEPING
THE KILLER DISTRACTED,
JUST SO HIS FRIENDS
COULD GET AWAY.
[BOTH]
HAHHHHH!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
HE KNOWS HE CAN'T WIN,
BUT HE'S DOING IT
FOR HIS FRIENDS.
[SOJIRO]
SEEING AS IT'S CHRISTMAS,
I THINK IT'S ONLY FITTING
THAT I GIVE YOU A LITTLE GIFT.
AKATSUKI, I WANT YOU
TO PAY ATTENTION TO THIS.
EH...
NOW OF COURSE,
SOME OF THESE TIPS
AREN'T GONNA BE
THAT HELPFUL TO YOU.
SWORD OF VOWS!
(BATTLE GRUNTS AND
SWORD CLASHING)
EHEHAHAHA! UWAH!
UWAH!
[SOJIRO] WATCH CAREFULLY,
AND LISTEN TO ME!
YOU MUST MAINTAIN AN ATTITUDE
OF CONSTANT IMPROVEMENT.
AND NEVER FOR A MOMENT DISCOUNT
TRAINING YOU'VE RECEIVED!
EHEAHAHAHA!
(GASP)
AKATSUKI, I KNOW IT'S NOT MUCH
AND I WISH I COULD FIND
A BETTER WAY TO EXPLAIN IT.
BUT THAT'S ALL THERE REALLY
IS TO THE ORAL ARTS!
[AKATSUKI]
WE'RE NOT DONE!
[NERURESU]
EHEH, HEHAHAHA...
[AKATSUKI] I DON'T, I DON'T FEEL
LIKE I'VE LEARNED ANYTHING!
BUT I, I FEEL LIKE I'M SO CLOSE!
(SCREAMING AND STRAINING)
[NAOTSUGU]
THIS CAN'T BE REAL! IT CAN'T!
[SHIROE]
AHHHHHHH! UWAAAA!
[NAOTSUGU]
SHIROE!
[BOTH]
WAHHHHHHHHHH!
(SHAKY BREATH)
I UNDERSTAND THERE'S
A TRADITIONAL ADVENTURER
GREETING FOR TODAY.
MERRY CHRISTMAS. (LAUGHING)
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING, RIGHT NOW?
(STRUGGLED BREATH)
I REALLY NEED TO SEE YOU...
MY LORD...
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] A WALK
THROUGH AN IMAGINARY CITY.
A PLACE WHERE SHE SEES A
REFLECTION OF HER OWN REGRETS
AND THE SCARS IN HER HEART.
RUNNING IN A STATE OF CONFUSION,
SHE FINDS HERSELF ON
A DISTANT SHORE.
WHILE SHE'S THERE, SHE FINDS
A WARM AND FAMILIAR FACE.
REUNITED IN THE WORLD OF DEATH,
THEY FIND COMFORT
IN ONE ANOTHER.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!