[WILLIAM]
HOW'S IT LOOK, AZAREA?
HE'S JUST KNELLING
THERE WILLIAM...
NO OTHER ENEMIES
ARE ON SIGHT.
[WILLIAM]
EXCELLENT!
[SHIROE] LET'S GET
THIS STARTED SHALL WE?!
(CHUCKLE)
LET'S GO.
[WILLIAM]
EVERYBODY REMEMBER THE PLAN?
(YELLING ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS)
[TETORA] GOT IT!
CAREFUL OUT THERE, NAOTSUGU!
WHATEVER! I'VE GOT THIS!
[NAOTSUGU AND DINKURON]
MHMM!
[SHIROE]
NAOTSUGU... TWENTY METERS AWAY!
[NAOTSUGU]
GOT IT!
CASTLE OF STONE!
[WILLIAM]
PERFECT! WELL DONE!
ALL RIGHT! THE TANK'S
GOT HIS ATTENTION!
(WAR CRY)
WAHHHHH!!!
[BOLOGNESE MASTER, VOICEOVER]
THE SKILL RUSEATO JUST USED,
"HARK! MOONLIT FUNERAL BELLS,"
[SASAMEYUKI] 11! 12! 13! 14! 15!
HAS A 90‐SECOND RECAST TIME.
[SASAMEYUKI] 16! 17!
[PROMETHEUS, VOICEOVER] THAT'S
NOT A LOT,
BUT WE CAN USE THAT TIME
TO GET INTO POSITION!
[WILLIAM, VOICEOVER]
THIS TIME, WE DO IT. LET'S GO!
[NAOTSUGU]
THERE YOU GO, FANCY PANTS!
JUST KEEP YOUR UGLY LITTLE
MUG POINTED AT ME!
[SASAMEYUKI] 23! 24! 25!
[WILLIAM] REAR GUARD! FALL BACK!
DAMAGE REPORT!
[SASAMEYUKI] 26! 27! 28! 29!
[SHIROE] HARDLY A SCRATCH!
WE NEED A BARRIER ON NAOTSUGU!
[SHIROE] KEEP IT STEADY GUYS!
WE NEED TO HIT IT
AT THE RIGHT TIME!
YAHHHH!!!!
[SHIROE] IF HE THROWS SOMETHING
AT YOU, DEFEND YOURSELF!
BUT WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T HIT RUSEATO UNLESS
YOU'RE THE ONE OF THE 9
DESIGNATED ATTACKERS!
WE NEED TO STICK TO THE PLAN!
[FEDERICO, VOICEOVER] HM?
SOMETHING'S CHANGED ABOUT HIM.
HE'S TALKING TO US MUCH
MORE THAN HE USED TO.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING TOGETHER
A LOT BETTER SINCE
WE WERE DEFEATED THE FIRST
TIME. WE'RE GROWING.
WE'VE BECOME TRUE
COMRADES‐IN‐ARMS.
AND I COULD NEVER FIGHT FOR
A MAN I DIDN'T RESPECT.
[DEMICAS]
LIGHTNING... STRAIGHT!
[FEDERICO, VOICEOVER] IN THE
END, ONE CANNOT AFFORD
TO HATE THEIR FELLOW WARRIORS.
[FEDERICO]
VIPER SLASH!
[FEDERICO, VOICEOVER] I'LL
ADMIT, SHIROE CAN BE WITHDRAWN
AND MAKE THINGS UNCOMFORTABLE
FOR EVERYONE SOMETIMES.
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU, SWITCH
OUT WITH DINKURON!
[NAOTSUGU] AIGHT!
[DINKURON] GOT IT!
[DINKURON, VOICEOVER]
BUT IF WE'RE HONEST,
IN THE GRAND SCHEME OF THINGS,
THAT'S A PRETTY MINOR PROBLEM.
[JUNZO, VOICEOVER] YEAH, WE'RE
ALL A BUNCH OF GAMERS
WITH BAD SOCIAL SKILLS.
COMES WITH THE TERRITORY.
(WAR CRY)
[HIGHLAND, VOICEOVER]
Y'KNOW, I STILL DON'T
WANT TO DIE OUT HERE.
[ELTON DISKA, VOICEOVER] EVERY
ONE OF US IS DOING THIS BECAUSE
WE CHOSE TO DO SO.
[MOLLUSCA TYPE @ AKIBA,
VOICEOVER] I'VE DIED MORE TIMES
THAN I CARE TO COUNT
IN THIS PLACE.
[UKIYO, VOICEOVER] AND EVERY
TIME, I ENDED UP STUCK IN THAT
HORRIBLE DREAM. BUT I'VE
NOTICED SOMETHING...
[TOKO, VOICEOVER] I'VE NEVER
SEEN A MEMBER OF SILVER SWORD
CAUGHT IN ONE OF THOSE DREAMS.
[PROROCCA, VOICEOVER]
YOU'RE RIGHT... NOT EVEN ONCE.
[PROMETHEUS, VOICEOVER] I'VE
NEVER HAD ANY REGRETS
CONCERNING ANY OF MY GUILDMATES!
[PIANISSISSIMO, VOICEOVER] THIS
IS WHAT IT MEANS
TO BELONG SOMEWHERE.
[FEDERICO, VOICEOVER] IT'S
DOWNRIGHT EMBARRASSING
FOR A MAN MY AGE TO
SAY THIS, BUT...
[BOLOGNESE MASTER, VOICEOVER]
I HAVE TO WONDER,
IF WE CAN CALL EACH
OTHER, "FRIENDS"
[ALL]
GAH!
[SHIROE]
RAGOMARU!
[RAGOMARU]
ON IT!
[RAGOMARU, VOICEOVER]
I WANT TO DO THIS!
[ENKARTANTO, VOICEOVER] I DON'T
CARE ANYMORE
ABOUT BEATING RAID BOSSES.
[KAWATARO, VOICEOVER] IT'S NOT
LIKE I WANT GLORY OR TREASURE...
[PROROCCA, VOICEOVER]
I JUST... WANT TO WIN!
[ELTON DISKA, VOICEOVER] THE
TIME WE'VE SPENT
HAS NOT BEEN A WASTE.
[ALL, VOICEOVER]
AND WE ARE GOING TO PROVE IT!
[RAGOMARU]
ZANTETSUKEN!
[SHIROE]
GET READY, WILLIAM!
[WILLIAM]
THIS IS IT!
SHIROE...! I NEED A
DISTRACTION FROM YOUR TEAM!
AAAAGH!!!
[DINKURON] REMEMBER, GUYS! BUILD
THEIR HATE AND LET 'EM HAVE IT!
DON'T LEAVE A SINGLE
ONE OF THEM ALIVE!
[ALL]
YEAH!
[VOINEN, THINKING] SHIROE'S
PLAN IS COMING TOGETHER.
LAST TIME, IBRA HABRA
AND TARTAURGA
DIDN'T SHOW UP UNTIL
AFTER THE GATES WENT UP.
AND NOW, THE GATES
ARE STILL CLOSED.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE ABLE TO MOVE.
THE SAME FOR RUSEATO!
WE'RE USING THE WEST
CORRIDOR THIS TIME AROUND!
THAT MEANS WE OUGHTA
BE ABLE TO DEAL
WITH IBRA HABRA ON
OUR OWN, RIGHT?!
YEAH, AND WE'RE ALREADY
CONFIRMED THAT THE GOAL
IS JUST PAST THE
HOLDING PEN AHEAD.
[VOINEN] OKAY, BUT WE STILL
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT RUSEATO
BUSTING DOWN THE GATE
AND COMING AFTER US.
[FEDERICO]YEAH, AND IF TARTAURGA
DECIDES TO GO THE LONG WAY,
HE COULD ALSO COME AFTER
US TO AID IBRA HABRA.
[BOLOGNESE MASTER] EVEN IF WE DO
MANAGE TO BEAT IBRA HABRA...
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE WE'D HAVE
TO DEAL WITH MORE
RAID BOSSES AFTER THAT!
WELL, I GUESS I'M KINDA WORRIED
ABOUT THAT... BUT STILL...
I THINK I'M LIKING OUR CHANCES
BETTER THIS TIME AROUND.
[PROMETHEUS] YEAH!
[PROROCCA] I DON'T CARE IF
IT'S FIFTEEN PERCENT
OR FIVE PERCENT!
[ENKARTANTO] ALRIGHT EVERYBODY,
COME ON!
WE GOTTA GO FOR IT... WE MIGHT
NOT GET ANOTHER SHOT AT THIS!
[DEMICAS, THINKING] I'LL BE
DAMNED IF HE ISN'T RIGHT
ABOUT THIS... BUT YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BE A GENIUS TO FIGURE IT OUT.
AND NO ONE OUT THERE GETS TO
PICK EXACTLY
HOW THEIR LIFE IS GONNA GO.
I COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT THAT
WHEN I WOUND UP IN THIS WORLD.
I THOUGHT SINCE I WAS IN A GAME,
I COULD DO WHATEVER I WANTED,
WHENEVER THE HELL I WANTED.
I FIGURED I COULD MAKE
ANYTHING GO MY WAY,
AND I GOT SENT TO THE
CATHEDRAL FOR MY TROUBLE.
THINGS DON'T ALWAYS
GO AS PLANNED.
WHETHER IT'S HERE
OR THE REAL WORLD!
I HAD TO LEARN
THAT THE HARD WAY.
AND THEN, JUST WHEN I THOUGHT
I HAD EVERYTHING ABOUT
THIS WORLD FIGURED OUT,
IT THREW ME ANOTHER CURVE...
[UPASHI] UGH. YOU ARE SUCH
A SLOB! [DEMICAS] EH!? UH?
[UPASHI]
DON'T YOU NEED TO BE SOMEWHERE?
[DEMICAS]
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
IF ALL YOU'RE GONNA
DO IS STAND THERE,
YOU'RE IN THE WAY!
SHUT UP, NPC!
YOU NEED TO KNOW
YOUR PLACE! UHUH?
HUMPH... DO YOU WANT THIS
HOUSE CLEANED UP OR NOT?
OTHERWISE WHY ARE YOU
KEEPING ME HERE?
[UPASHI] RELEASE ME,
KILL ME, OR MOVE IT!
I CAN'T CLEAN LIKE THIS!
UH... OKAY...
[DEMICAS, THINKING] THAT WAS
ANOTHER PLAN GONE WRONG.
AND, I LOST TO SILVER SWORD.
IT TORE MY GUILD APART.
THEN THOSE RAID BOSSES GOT ME.
I EVEN LOST TO WILLIAM
AS A GUILD MASTER!
HIS ENTIRE TEAM GOT THE
HELL BEAT OUT OF THEM
AND NO ONE IN HIS
GUILD LEFT HIS SIDE!
NOT A SINGLE DESERTER!
[TETORA] SHIROE, LOOK BEHIND
IBRA HABRA. IS THAT IT?
[SHIROE] THAT'S RIGHT.
OUR TARGET FOR THE RAID IS
JUST AT THE END OF THE HALL.
(HISSES AND SNARLS)
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAAAAUGH!
ANCHOR HOWL!
(ROAR)
[WILLIAM] CONCENTRATE
HEALING ON THE MAIN TANK!
[PIANISSISSIMO] I'M RAISING
HIS FIRE RESISTANCE.
[PROMETHEUS] LET HIM HAVE IT!
WITH ELEMENTAL ICE, WATER,
AND WIND ATTACKS!
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU, WE NEED A
CLEAR SHOT THROUGH THE CORRIDOR!
GET HIM OFF THAT SOUTHWEST WALL!
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH!
FORTRESS STANCE!
I THINK I'M GONNA TEST OUT THESE
NEW WEAPONS
BY TAKING OFF YOUR HEAD!
[NAOTSUGU, VOICEOVER] FORTRESS
STANCE IS GREAT FOR DEFENSE,
BUT IT REALLY WREAKS HAVOC WITH
MY MOBILITY AND ACCURACY.
[DEMICAS]
GIMME A CRACK AT HIM!
[NAOTSUGU]
HUH?
[DEMICAS]
YAH!
[DEMICAS, THINKING] I'VE HAD
ABOUT ALL THE HUMILIATION
I CAN TAKE!
THAT ENCHANTER'S CASTING
KEEN EDGE ON ME AGAIN.
[SHIROE]
ISN'T THAT...?
EVERYBODY TAKE COVER NOW!
[WILLIAM]
SCATTER!
[DEMICAS]
NOT ON MY WATCH!
[FEDERICO]
(REACTION) WAIT, WHAT?
[TETORA]
IT'S LIKE A SAUNA!
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
COVERING...
IT'S A SKILL THAT ALLOWS A
PLAYER TO TAKE THE DAMAGE
FOR NEARBY TEAM MEMBERS.
[WILLIAM] THAT WAS A
GOOD MOVE, DEMICAS. NICE.
(GROWL)
[DEMICAS]
IT'S GETTIN' HOT OVER HERE!
[NAOTSUGU, VOICEOVER] MONKS HAVE
A HIGHER RESISTANCE
TO ELEMENTAL ATTACKS.
THEY ALSO HAVE HIGHER
OVERALL HIT POINTS.
IF WE KEEP SPLITTING THE DAMAGE,
I WON'T NEED TO SWAP OUT OF THE
FRONT LINE! IN OTHER WORDS,
I CAN KEEP THIS UP ALL DAY!
[WILLIAM] WELL DONE! KEEP
HITTING HIM ON HIS LEFT FLANK!
(ROAR)
[NAOTSUGU]
COME AND GET ME, UGLY!
THERE'S A LOT MORE
WHERE THAT CAME FROM!
[TETORA] (SQUEAL) NAOTSUGU, YOU
SURE ARE HYPED UP, AREN'TCHA?!
[NAOTSUGU]
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED!
(GIGGLE)
[TETORA]
WHOO...! IT'S MY TURN!
HANG ON EVERYBODY!
YOUR SUPER STARLET HEALER
IS HERE TO SAVE THE DAY!
AURORA HEAL!
[JUNZO] NOW THAT...
WAS GOOD TIMING.
AH YES, NOW WE'RE TALKIN'!
THAT FEELS GREAT!
[TETORA]
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME!
[NAOTSUGU] THAT GOT
'EM PERKED UP!
WHAT ELSE WOULD YOU EXPECT
FROM A GORGEOUS SPARKLY ANGEL?!
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THOSE GUYS?
THEY AREN'T VERY
SERIOUS, ARE THEY?
(LAUGHS)
BE HONEST, HAVE YOU
FALLEN FOR ME YET?!
THAT'D BE A "NO."
[TETORA]
(GIGGLES) AW, YOU'RE NO FUN!
OH, YEAH! I JUST REMEMBERED
THERE WAS SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO TELL YOU!
[NAOTSUGU] EARTH TO SPACE CASE!
KINDA BUSY OVER HERE!
[TETORA] YOU'RE GONNA
LOVE IT! ARE YOU READY?
I'M JOINING LOG HORIZON!
WHADDYA THINK!
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT?!
(GIGGLE)
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
CAUSE I ABSOLUTELY POSITIVELY
CAN'T KEEP MYSELF AWAY FROM YOU!
AND DON'T WORRY,
I GOT SHIROE'S PERMISSION FIRST!
BOOTY, BOOTY DANCE!
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE, BUDDY...
YOU'RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS.
(ROAR)
[TETORA]
UH, THAT LOOKS KINDA BAD!
[WILLIAM]
FRONTLINE, PULL BACK! FEDERICO!
WE NEED FIRE RESISTANCE!
EVERYONE ELSE, GIVE ME
BARRIERS AND HEALING!
[AZAREA]
HUH? OH MY GOD!
(GASP)
(SNARL)
[SHIROE AND WILLIAM]
TARTAURGA?!
[ELTON DISKA]
IT'S TARTAURGA!
[HIGHLAND]
(SQUEAK) THERE HE IS!
[BOLOGNESE MASTER]
STEADY, EVERYONE!
[WILLIAM]
DINKURON!
[DINKURON]
IT'S PAYBACK TIME!
I FELL BACK FROM
THE FRONT LINES,
JUST TO MAKE SURE I HAD A
SHOT TO FINISH YOU OFF!
[WILLIAM]
HEALERS, GET INTO FORMATION!
[ALL]
ROGER!
[DINKURON]
CASTLE OF STONE!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
IBRA HABRA AND TARTAURGA...
WE CAN'T REALLY EXPECT TO
BEAT BOTH OF THEM AT ONCE.
[WILLIAM] SO WHAT WAS IT YOU
SAID ABOUT
A FIFTEEN PERCENT
CHANCE OF VICTORY?
THE LAST TIME WE WERE HERE...
BOTH IBRA HABRA AND TARTAURGA
ATTACKED US AT THE SAME TIME.
WE DON'T STAND A CHANCE
IF THAT HAPPENS AGAIN.
[WILLIAM]
YES, I WOULD AGREE.
[SHIROE] SO WHAT IF WE TOOK ONE
OF THEM OUT OF THE PICTURE?
[JUNZO]
WE COULD'VE WON THAT FIGHT...
[ORDISSO]
JUST WHAT IS HE GETTING AT...?
IF WE'RE ABLE TO KEEP THEM FROM
HAVING OVERLAPPING
ATTACK FIELDS,
WE MAY HAVE A CHANCE.
[WILLIAM]
HMM...
[SHIROE]
THE CAVERN IS THE RIGHT SIZE...
BUT SPACE WILL BE GETTING REALLY
TIGHT IN THERE
SO WATCH YOURSELVES.
WE'VE GOTTA KEEP
'EM BOTH APART.
I NEED NAOTSUGU TO DRAW IBRA
HABRA TO THE SOUTH‐WESTERN WALL.
DINKURON WILL KEEP TARTAURGA
AT THE ENTRANCE
OF THE NORTH‐EASTERN CORRIDOR.
NOW, WHATEVER YOU DO,
DON'T GET COMPLACENT ABOUT
STAYING IN ONE PLACE.
NAOTSUGU AND DINKURON ARE BOTH
GONNA NEED TWO HEALERS
DEDICATED TO KEEPING
THEIR HIT POINTS UP.
WE'LL REDEPLOY THE OTHER
HEALERS TO HELP EVERYONE ELSE.
SPACE IS THE ISSUE HERE.
TOO CLOSE AND YOU'RE
GETTING HIT ON ALL SIDES.
TOO FAR AWAY, AND THE REST OF
THE PARTY
CAN'T SUPPORT YOU WITH
HEALING AND BARRIERS.
EVERYONE IN THE REAR NEEDS TO
WATCH HOW THE RAID BOSSES MOVE,
SO YOU CAN ADJUST YOUR
INTERVAL SPACING.
WE'LL BE WALKING ON A
TIGHTROPE THE ENTIRE BATTLE.
A STRING IF YOU ASK ME...
IT'S GONNA BE PRETTY TOUGH.
BUT I TELL YOU WHAT, I LIKE IT!
FEDERICO, I NEED AN ATTACK RANGE
AND POWER DAMPENER OUT THERE!
[FEDERICO]
YOU GOT IT!
[SHIROE] I NEED MORE HEALING
POWER FROM YOU, TETORA!
[TETORA] I'M ALREADY GIVING
YOU EVERYTHING I GOT OKAY!
[SHIROE]
HANG ON!
[TETORA]
AWW! THAT'S REALLY CUTE!
[SHIROE]
FORCE STEP!
OH, WOW! I REALLY LOOK
LIKE A STARLET, NOW!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] FORCE STEP
REDUCES A PLAYER'S RECAST
BY NEARLY HALF FOR
A FULL MINUTE.
THIS INCREASES A MAGIC
USER'S CASTING OPTIONS.
IT CUTS AURORA HEAL'S USUAL 600
SECOND RECAST TIME
DOWN TO 480 SECONDS.
AND IN A FIGHT LIKE THIS,
2 MINUTES IS A WORLD
OF DIFFERENCE.
SPEAKING OF...
[SHIROE]
MANA CHANNELING!
[SHIROE, THINKING] KNOWING THAT
SHE CAN CAST MORE SPELLS,
MEANS SHE'S ALSO
LOSING MAGIC POINTS.
MANA CHANNELING GIVES HER BACK
SOME OF THAT POWE
R WHEN I SHARE MY MANA.
THANKS, SHIROE! MWAH!
[SHIROE]
YEP!
UH... AH!
[VOINEN]
OVER HERE!
[SHIROE]
UH!
(SURPRISED)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
THE SEQUOIA OF LIFE.
A SUMMONING SPELL
USED BY DRUIDS.
ANY PARTY MEMBER TOUCHED BY
THE GLOW OF THE TREE
GETS PARTIAL HEALING.
AND RIGHT NOW, THEY NEED ALL
THE HIT POINTS THEY CAN GET.
[TETORA]
AWESOME!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
THAT TREE CAN GIVE 10 PLAYERS
UP TO THIRTY PERCENT
OF THEIR HEALTH BACK!
[SHIROE]
KARMA DRIVE!
(ROAR)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
BASED ON OUR COUNTS,
IT LOOKS LIKE IBRA HABRA
CAN CAST MERCILESS BANQUET
IN PURGATORY ONCE
EVERY THREE MINUTES.
KNOWING THAT, I'M GONNA HAVE
VOINEN CAST MARSH RAIN
AND LIFE BURST AT THE SAME
TIME TO WARD IT OFF.
AND INCREASE IBRA HABRA'S
RECAST TIME TO 6 MINUTES.
ALSO, THAT'LL GIVE NAOTSUGU THAT
CHANCE
TO RECAST CASTLE OF STONE,
SO HE CAN STAY ON THE FRONT LINE
AND KEEP DOING DAMAGE TO HIM.
AND IN THOSE NINE MINUTES,
TETORA WILL BE ABLE TO RECAST
ANOTHER AURORA HEAL AND GET
EVERYONE'S HIT‐POINTS BACK UP.
ALSO, I JUST CAST KARMA DRIVE,
WHICH WILL ALLOW EVERYONE WHO
DEALS A CRITICAL HIT ON
IBRA HABRA TO REGAIN SOME
OF THEIR MAGIC POINTS BACK.
IF WE STICK TO THE PLAN, AND
THERE ARE NO MORE SURPRISES,
WE CAN FINISH HIM OFF IN
JUST UNDER TWELVE MINUTES.
AND AFTER THAT, WE
CAN FOCUS OUR ENERGY
TO PRESSING THE
ATTACK ON TARTAURGA!
THIS...
... WILL WORK!
[SHIROE] KEEP ON
ATTACKING HIM, YOU GUYS!
WE CAN WIN THIS
THING IN 12 MINUTES!
[WILLIAM]
YOU HEARD THE MAN!
THE VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES
SAYS WE CAN WIN THIS!
KEEP ON FIGHTING OUT THERE!
DON'T LET HIM RECOVER!
[ALL]
YEAH!
(SHOCKED)
[ENKARTANTO]
NO! NO WAY!
[AZAREA]
NOT NOW!
[UKIYO]
OH MAN, THIS ISN'T GOOD!
[TOKO]
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
THE SHADOW VANGUARDS...
SO, WE'VE GOT AS MANY
VANGUARDS AS THERE WERE PLAYERS
WHO DID DAMAGE TO RUSEATO WHEN
HE WAS IN BLACK KNIGHT FORM.
PERHAPS THESE ARE SOME
WE DIDN'T GET EARLIER.
I COULD'VE SWORN WE TOOK
CARE OF ALL OF THEM
WHEN WE FOUGHT OUR WAY HERE.
THE OTHER THING IS,
EVEN IF HE SWITCHES
BACK TO BLACK KNIGHT FORM,
THERE'S NO ONE IN HIS
ZONE TO HURT HIM...
WAIT A MINUTE...! THAT'S CRAZY!
HE ATTACKED HIMSELF TO
MAKE MORE OF THOSE THINGS?!
THERE'S NO TELLING HOW MANY
TIMES HE CAN DO THAT.
WAIT A MINUTE...
HE'S GONNA USE HIS BLACK KNIGHT
MODE TO KEEP INJURING HIMSELF
AND SENDING MORE OF THOSE
VANGUARDS AFTER US!
HOW MANY ARE THERE NOW?!
IF HE USES ALL HIS
HEALTH EVERY 200 SECONDS
TO SPAWN AS MANY VANGUARDS AS
HE CAN, HOW WILL THEY MULTIPLY?
31? 62? WHAT'RE WE FACING?
31 OF THEM WOULD STILL
GIVE US A FIGHTING CHANCE.
WE JUST NEED ANOTHER 10 MINUTES
TO FINISH OFF IBRA HABRA.
[SHIROE] FRONT LINE!
[SHIROE, THINKING] I NEED
SOMEONE TO LEAD THE
VANGUARDS OUTTA HERE.
SO THE REST OF US CAN
TAKE IBRA HABRA DOWN!
IF SOMEONE CAN JUST
GET THEIR ATTENTION!
SOMEONE KITE THE VANGUARDS!
[JUNZO]
YEAH, I'M ON IT. HUH?
[DEMICAS]
HYAAHHH!
WYVERN KICK!
[SHIROE]
UH...
[WILLIAM]
DEMICAS!
[DEMICAS]
TAUNTING SHOUT!
[NAOTSUGU]
SERIOUSLY?
[TETORA]
DEMI‐POO'S THE COOLEST!
[DEMICAS] HEH! C'MON YA PUKES!
JUST TRY AND HIT ME! (LEAP)
(SURPRISE)
(SNARL)
[SHIROE]
EH...?
WHOA! HEY! WAIT A MINUTE!
[NAOTSUGU]
SHIROE!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?! WAAUGUGUH!
SHUT THE HELL UP, FOUR EYES!
[SHIROE] WHA?
[DEMICAS] WYVERN KICK!
YAH!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
IS HE REALLY TRYING TO GET
BACK AT ME
BY SABOTAGING THE
RAID?! HUH...?
WAIT A MINUTE. I THINK I SEE
WHAT HE'S DOING.
THEY'RE FOLLOWING US.
[SHIROE]
MENTAL LIGHTNING!
[SHIROE, THINKING] I SUPPOSE IF
I CAN USE MYSELF
LIKE A CANNON
STRAPPED TO HIS BACK.
I CAN MAKE THIS WORK!
[SHIROE] HEAD TO THE
CORRIDOR BY TARTAUGA!
[DEMICAS] DON'T GIVE ME ORDERS,
YOU LITTLE BRAINIAC NERD!
[SHIROE]
THAT SPELL...
HE'S USING WHITE NIGHT! HE'S
GONNA FREEZE US!
[DEMICAS]
YEAH, NOT MEEE!
LYNX TUMBLING!
(HEAVY BREATHING)
[WILLIAM]
WHAT DO YOU NEED, SHIROE!
[SHIROE]
WILLIAM! A LITTLE HELP HERE!
[WILLIAM]
RIGHT...
HM.
(CHEERING)
[TETORA] GO FOR IT, DEMI‐POO!
[FEDERICO] GO VILLAIN
BEHIND GLASSES!
[SHIROE]
MIND SHOCK!
ASTRAL BIND!
[SHIROE, THINKING] WELL, IT
LOOKS LIKE IT'S WORKING SO FAR.
BUT...
I'M NOT SURE WHAT
HE'S REALLY UP TO.
THE FIRST TIME WE MET,
I COULDN'T STAND THE GUY...
I GUESS ACTING LIKE A
TOTAL JERK WAS HIS WAY OF
DEALING WITH BEING TRAPPED HERE.
IT'S NATURAL I GUESS...
HUMAN NATURE FOR SOME...
BUT I COULDN'T
ALLOW HIM TO DO IT.
UH? SLOW DOWN! THERE AREN'T
ANY MORE VANGUARDS BEHIND US!
WE NEED TO LET 'EM CATCH UP!
IF WE LET THEM GET BACK TO THE
CAVE THEN WE'RE DOING
ALL THIS RUNNING FOR NOTHING!
WHAT'S GOING ON,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
I'M SERIOUS! WHOA! (EXHALE)
EH?
[DEMICAS] LISTEN, BOY...
YOU WILL CALL ME BY MY NAME.
MMMPH...
[SHIROE]
I...
UH...
(EXHALE)
MMN.
DEMICAS.
THAT SO HARD?
DEMICAS, YOU CAN
BE A REAL JERK,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YEAH, WELL Y'KNOW...
IT'S NOT LIKE I REALLY
LIKE YOU EITHER.
[SHIROE]
SO‐‐ WAIT, WHOA! WHOA!
(GRUNTING)
OW!
[DEMICAS]
LOOK FOUR‐EYES...
YOU WANNA DIE SO BAD,
THEN DO IT ON THE OTHER SIDE.
HEH... I AIN'T DYING
HERE. I GOT OTHER PLANS.
"OTHER SIDE"?
OH?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT...
HE TOOK ME TO THE INNERMOST
CHAMBER IN THE ABYSSAL SHAFT!
HE KNEW IT ALL THE TIME...!
I'M IMPRESSED!
(EXHALE)
[KINJO]
MASTER SHIROE, WELCOME.
I ONLY SAY THAT OUT
OF COURTESY, OF COURSE.
[SHIROE]
HMPH...
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] UPON
REACHING THE INNERMOST CHAMBER
OF THE ABYSSAL SHAFT...
THERE IS A SLUMBERING
RIVER OF GOLD.
THE FINAL RAID BOSS, ULLR
OF THE NINTH GARDEN,
LIES IN WAIT ALONG WITH
KINJO OF THE KUNIE TRIBE.
SHIROE TELLS HIM HIS
TRUE INTENTIONS...
BUT WHAT COULD THEY BE.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!