(LOW GROWL)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
A RAID PARTY
IS A MASSIVE ASSAULT ON AN
OBJECTIVE BY A LARGE GROUP
OF ADVENTURERS THAT
GOES ABOVE AND BEYOND
THE USUAL PARTY OF SIX.
THE MOST COMMON RAID PARTY
IS THE FULL RAID,
WHICH TAKES
FOUR GROUPS OF SIX
AND COMBINES THEM
INTO ONE FIGHTING UNIT.
THIS LET'S THE
PLAYERS EXPERIENCE
A FULL RANGE OF COMBAT AS WELL
AS GET THE BEST REWARDS.
HOWEVER, YOU CAN'T JUST
HAVE HIGH‐LEVEL PLAYERS
WITH OUTSTANDING EQUIPMENT
TO MAKE A GOOD RAID PARTY.
YOU MUST ANALYZE YOUR ENEMY AND
HAVE A WELL‐PLANNED STRATEGY.
OF COURSE,
THE PLAYERS YOU CHOOSE
HAVE TO HAVE SOLID TEAMWORK
TO PULL THE RAID OFF.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU CAN JUST
PICK A BUNCH OF RANDOM PEOPLE
AND GO FOR IT.
AND IT DOESN'T HURT IF
THE MEMBERS OF YOUR PARTY
HAVE ALREADY EXPERIENCED
DEATH AND RESURRECTION TOGETHER.
[NAOTSUGU] OKAY, SO WHO DO
WE CALL FOR HELP?
I THINK I HAVE SOMEONE IN MIND.
[NAOTSUGU]
DUDE, REALLY?
[REGAN]
THIS FORTIFICATION ONCE STOOD
AS A DEFENSE AGAINST
ALL MANNER OF GIANTS...
IT'S WHY THE EZZO
EMPIRE BUILT SUSUKINO.
[NAOTSUGU] HMMM? NOT SEEING
ANY GUARDS OUT HERE ANYMORE.
I'M HOPING THAT'S A GOOD THING.
[SHIROE] SIX MONTHS CAN
CHANGE A LOT, SO IT SEEMS.
WELL IF I DON'T SEE YOU BACK
PRETTY SOON, GOOD LUCK!
[SHIROE]
OKAY.
SAME TO YOU.
[NAOTSUGU]
PFFFT. YOU KNOW ME.
[WILLIAM] WELL, WELL.
NOW ISN'T THIS A TREAT?
[SHIROE] MISTER MASSACHUSETTS...
HOW'RE THINGS GOING HERE?
DON'T BE SO FORMAL,
JUST CALL ME "WILLIAM".
[SHIROE] FEEL FREE TO
CALL ME "SHIROE" THEN.
HMMM...
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
SILVER SWORD,
A RAID GUILD,
RANKING RIGHT UP WITH D. D. D.
AND THE BLACK SWORD KNIGHTS
FOR PURE COMBAT POWER.
WE ASKED WILLIAM TO ATTEND
THE FIRST MEETING
ESTABLISHING THE
ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE.
WE WANTED TO GET SILVER SWORD
ONBOARD WITH OUR EFFORTS.
HOWEVER...
[WILLIAM] YOU WANT TO LIVE
HERE AND TRY TO DEAL WITH
ALL ITS LITTLE ISSUES,
THEN FEEL FREE.
IT'S ACTUALLY CHARMING THAT YOU
THINK YOU CAN TALK IT ALL OUT.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DO IT WITHOUT US.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] THEY DECIDED
TO MOVE TO SUSUKINO,
IN SEARCH OF RAIDS MORE
WORTHY OF THEIR SKILLS.
NOW THEIR ABSENCE FROM
AKIHABARA MAKES THEM PERFECT.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE I CAN TURN TO.
I JUST HOPE HE AGREES THIS TIME.
OTHERWISE, I MAY RUN OUT
OF OPTIONS RATHER FAST.
I HAVE COME TO SPEAK TO YOU,
ONE GUILD MASTER TO ANOTHER.
I WOULD LIKE TO ASK
A FAVOR OF YOU.
[WILLIAM]
ALL RIGHT. WE'LL DO IT.
[SHIROE] UH?
YOU'VE COME
A LONG WAY TO SEE ME.
YOU MUST NEED HELP WITH A TASK
ONLY SILVER SWORD CAN COMPLETE.
AND IT'D BE PRETTY LOW CLASS
OF ME TO SAY NO
TO SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[SHIROE]
I APPRECIATE IT.
[WILLIAM]
WELL...
IT'S A FULL PARTY RAID,
AND I NEED ALL OF YOU.
THE DESTINATION IS
A NEW RAID ZONE
DOWN IN THE LOWEST LEVELS
OF THE DEPTHS OF PALM.
A FULLY PARTY RAID...
AND THAT MEANS WE CAN ONLY
GO IN THERE WITH 24 PLAYERS.
WE NEED OUR BEST PEOPLE,
BUT NOT EVERYONE WE HAVE.
WE WILL BE NEEDING
ADVANCE RECON OF THE AREA.
I HAVE ALREADY
TAKEN CARE OF THAT.
REALLY?
[NAOTSUGU]
IT'S CRAZY DOWN THERE!
[REGAN]
IMPRESSIVE, I'D SAY!
[SHIROE] WE'LL STOP HERE
FOR TODAY. LET'S GET BACK.
[NAOTSUGU]
DEFINITELY.
REGAN]
THAT'S AMAZING!
I'VE NEVER SEEN SO MANY
MONSTERS IN ONE PLACE.
[SHIROE] NOT TO MENTION
THEY'RE LEVEL 89 OR BETTER.
I'M PRETTY SURE
THERE ISN'T GOING TO BE
AN EASY PART OF THIS RAID.
SO WHAT DID YOU SEE?
THE TOP LEVEL
HAD SLIME MONSTERS,
AND THEY WERE EASILY
FIVE METERS ACROSS.
NOW, I'M ONLY
THINKING OUT LOUD HERE,
BUT BASED ON THE ORAL TRADITIONS
AND THE LAYOUT OF
THIS "SHAFT" STRUCTURE...
I GET THE FEELING WE'RE GOING
TO BE FACING MYTHICAL BEASTS.
ALRIGHT.
SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
WORKING OUT OF
SUSUKINO AS A BASE,
WE'VE GOTTEN USED TO
SUCH ADVERSARIES.
HOWEVER, MY GUILD ISN'T
AS STRONG AS YOU'D THINK.
HUH?
(EXHALES)
[NAOTSUGU] YOU EVER BEEN
HERE BEFORE, OLD TIMER?
[REGAN] OH MANY TIMES!
I HEARD THINGS FELL APART
AFTER THE "APOCALYPSE",
BUT IT SEEMS BETTER NOW...
I'M BETTING HAVING THE SILVER
SWORD AROUND HAS HELPED A LOT.
YOU CAN TELL THEY'RE A RAID
GUILD WITH A LOT OF DISCIPLINE.
'COURSE, I'D TAKE THESE GUYS
INSTEAD OF THOSE
BRIGANDIA LOSERS ANY DAY.
[REGAN]
THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
WHERE DO YOU SUPPOSE
THOSE HOODLUMS WENT?
I'M SORRY,
BUT WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
[WILLIAM] WE DON'T EXACTLY
HAVE THE NUMBER OF PLAYERS
NEEDED TO BE
UP AND RUNNING.
WE'RE KIND OF JUST A
NAME RIGHT NOW.
[SHIROE]
EH...?
I'M PRETTY SURE
I WON'T BE ABLE TO GET
EVERYONE TO COME
WITH US...
YOU MUST HAVE NOTICED A NUMBER
OF PEOPLE SQUATTING IN GUILDS
JUST TO KEEP THEMSELVES
SAFE FROM ENEMIES OR MONSTERS.
IN OTHER WORDS,
THEY'VE BASICALLY RETIRED.
THEY MIGHT BE UP
FOR A MILD RAID,
BUT NOTHING THAT PUTS
THEM IN REAL DANGER.
AND THIS RAID YOU'VE
COME TO ME WITH,
IT COULD BE THE TOUGHEST THE
SYSTEM'S EVER PUT TOGETHER.
WE NEED LEVEL NINETY‐FIVES, AND
WE'LL BE LUCKY TO GET TWENTY.
SO TELL ME, ARE THEY TRYING
TO PROTECT THEIR MEMORIES?
[WILLIAM] HMMM... POSSIBLY...
I'VE NEVER HEARD ANYONE
SAY ANYTHING OUT LOUD
ABOUT IT BEFORE.
MOST OF MY PEOPLE THINK IT'S
A RIDICULOUS IDEA ANYWAY.
SO IT'S NOT LIKE
THEY'RE AFRAID OF IT.
I'M NOT SURE
I UNDERSTAND.
HOW MANY TIMES HAVE YOU
DIED SINCE YOU GOT HERE?
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE?
I HAVEN'T... REALLY BEEN
THROUGH IT YET.
I'M NOT SURE I CAN
EXPLAIN IT, BUT I'LL TRY.
YOU LEARN A LOT
ABOUT YOURSELF...
YOU LEARN THINGS
THAT YOU WANTED TO KNOW
AND THINGS YOU
DIDN'T WANNA KNOW.
AND IT DOESN'T GET EASIER
EACH TIME IT HAPPENS EITHER.
SO MOST OF US DON'T WANNA
GO THROUGH IT AGAIN.
(DOORS SLAM OPEN)
[SHIROE] HM?
[WOMAN] OOHHH, YOU'D BETTER
NOT MESS WITH HIM...
[MAN]
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
[DEMICAS] WELL, IF IT ISN'T
SHIROE THE ENCHANTER.
YOU'VE GOT A LOTTA NERVE
SHOWING YOUR FACE AROUND HERE!
HMPH.
(ANGRY GRUNT)
[REGAN] DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT WILL BE EASY TO FIND
NEW PARTY MEMBERS?
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE'S
TAKING CARE OF MOST OF IT,
BUT I HAVE TO FIND A
FEW MYSELF, JUST IN CASE.
WHAT KIND OF PEOPLE
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
I'M KINDA PLAYIN' IT
BY EAR, YOU KNOW?
THAT HARDLY TELL ME
ANYTHING, MASTER!
I CAN'T EXPLAIN IT TO YOU
IN YOUR MAGICKY TALK.
I JUST NEED SOME DUDES,
KEEP AN EYE OUT.
I WAS THINKING
OF HELPING YOU,
BUT THAT'S PROBABLY
NOT A GOOD IDEA.
THEN WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TAKE CARE OF THINGS
AROUND HERE?
(CHUCKLES)
THAT WORKS FOR ME!
MY SKILLS AS A RESEARCHER
ARE BETTER SUITED
TO FINDING OUT WHAT'S
GOING ON IN THIS CITY.
[TETORA] AW, DANGIT!
[BOTH] HM?
[NAOTSUGU]
NICE PANTIES!
WELL FOR ONCE
I MUST AGREE WITH YOU.
A FELLOW
PANTY FAN, NICE!
I AM INDEED!
I UNDERSTAND ADVENTURERS ALSO
REFER TO THEM AS "BLOOMERS" OR
PANTALOONS OR
"HOT PANTS," IF YOU WILL.
IF YOU'LL PARDON ME,
IT SEEMS SUCH NAMES
MIGHT DISPARAGE
SOMETHING SO DELIGHTFUL.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I HOLD THEM IN THE
HIGHEST REGARD!
AS A TRUE ADMIRER OF
LADY'S UNDERWEAR I CAN‐
WAUUUGHHHH!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT, SIR?
[AKATSUKI] I GUESS THAT'S
ENOUGH PRACTICE FOR TODAY.
[NAOTSUGU] WH‐WHAT WAS THAT?!
THE LITTLE SHRIMP
PUT A CURSE ON ME.
A CURSE? WHAT DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT?
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME ABOUT IT,
AND DON'T LEAVE OUT ANY
DETAILS, IF YOU PLEASE.
[NAOTSUGU]
YOU'RE WAY TOO HAPPY, DUDE!
[TETORA]
GET ME OUTTA HERE, YOU MORONS!
AH!
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOUR FINE CURVES
DISTRACTED US.
IT'D BE A CRYING SHAME FOR ALL
MY LOVE‐STRUCK FANS OUT THERE
IF MY BEAUTIFUL FACE WAS
BLEMISHED IN A SNOW BANK.
DID SHE ACTUALLY SAY THAT?
IT WOULD APPEAR OUR NEW FRIEND
IS QUITE FULL OF HERSELF.
GAH!
YOU KNOW WHAT, GRAMPS?
THE MORE I GET
TO KNOW YA,
THE MORE I'M STARTING
TO LIKE YA! HAHA
THE FEELING IS MUTUAL.
UH‐HUH!
I CAN HEAR YOU, Y'KNOW!
HUH?
AH, SHE'S RECOVERED.
I'M TETORA, THE STAR
SHINING IN THE NIGHT SKY!
SYMBOL OF DIVINE BEAUTY...
THE GALAXY‐STYLE STARLET!
OR JUST "TETORA",
IF YOU'RE IN A HURRY.
TETORA, HUH?
HM... SURE,
YOU MIGHT BE CUTE
AND EVERYTHING...
BUT THERE'S NO WAY IN
HELL I'M ADMITTING TO IT
WHEN YOU'RE ALL
STUCK UP LIKE THAT.
IF I HAD TO TAKE INTO
ACCOUNT EVERYTHING
I'M SEEING AND HEARING
FROM YOU SO FAR...
THERE'S NO CONTEST!
THE WOMAN OF MY DREAMS...
IS THE LOVELY AND
GRACIOUS MARIELLE!
MARIELLE! MARIELLE!
[BOTH]
HUH?
UH, SORRY
'BOUT THAT...
[NAOTSUGU]
HERE YOU GO.
OKAY, THANKS...
[NAOTSUGU] INTERESTING,
SHE'S LEVELED UP TO 92,
JUST LIKE ME AND SHIROE
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE.
[NAOTSUGU] SHE MIGHT NOT BE
THAT BAD, ACTUALLY.
LOOK, MISTER...
I KNOW I DO A LOT TO KEEP
MYSELF LOOKING AMAZING...
BUT YOU NEED TO STOP STARING.
I WASN'T
STARING AT YOU!
OH I KNOW YOU
CAN'T HELP IT.
GORGEOUS HOTTIES LIKE
ME ARE CONSTANTLY
SPEWING OUT PHEROMONES,
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?!
FACE IT, YOU KNOW YOU WANT ME
WHENEVER YOU SMELL ME.(HUMS)
THIS MIGHT BE A BAD
TIME TO TELL YOU,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE EMITTING
SOMETHING OTHER
THAN PHEROMONES.
ACK!
OH MAN! NOW THAT'S
WHAT I CALL A ZINGER!
CHALK ONE UP
FOR STINKY!
[TETORA] STARLETS DO NOT
DO SUCH THINGS, SIR!
[TETORA] THAT WAS VERY IMPOLITE
OF YOU, YOU WRINKLED OLD TOAD!
DID YOU CALL ME A TOAD?!
AND SINCE YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY
IN LOVE WITH ME,
I'LL LET YOU CARRY ME,
MISTER ARMOR.
[NAOTSUGU]
H‐HEY! GET OFF! WHA‐
EH‐HEHH! I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, I JUST LOVE SEEING
HOW MEN FREAK OUT
AND GET ALL GOOEY AND STUPID
WHENEVER I RUB
ALL OVER THEM. Y'KNOW...
AND YOU BETTER
MIND YOUR MANNERS,
I DON'T LIKE IT WHEN GUYS
DO IT BACK TO ME!
[NAOTSUGU] ERK! IF YOU DON'T
LIKE IT, DON'T DO IT!
[TETORA] ALLEY‐OOP
[NAOTSUGU] WOAH!
(GIGGLE)
[NAOTSUGU, MUFFLED]
OKAY, FINE, YOU'RE IN...
HUH?
ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S A WISE IDEA?
REMEMBER I'M GOING
WITH MY GUT HERE.
HMM?
(SEETHING)
[VOINEN]
I THINK THEY'LL BE FINE.
[FEDERICO] THIS MIGHT BE A GOOD
TIME TO TAKE A BREAK OUT BACK.
[WAITRESS]
UH! (EXHALES)
HMPH.
[DEMICAS] LISTEN TO ME
YOU ARROGANT PRICK...
WE'VE GOT UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
[DEMICAS] LAST WE MET,
YOU WERE HAVING SOME
TROUBLE WITH MY NAME.
REMEMBER IT NOW?
[SHIROE] OF COURSE I DO,
MISTER DUMMY FACE.
[DEMICAS] WELL GET OUTTA THAT
CHAIR! WE'RE TAKIN' IT OUTSIDE!
[SHIROE] OH, I THINK
I'M FINE RIGHT HERE.
I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR THIS.
[WILLIAM] KNOCK IT OFF, DEMICAS.
[DEMICAS] HUH?
SHIROE'S HERE AS
MY GUEST, UNDERSTAND?
I DON'T GIVE A DAMN...!
I'M GONNA MAKE HIM PAY‐
[WILLIAM]
HE DEFEATED YOU, RIGHT?
UWAH! (GRUNT)
YOU HAD A FIGHT.
YOU LOST.
YOU GOT RESURRECTED.
GET OVER IT.
COME ON!
I HAVEN'T HAD MY EXERCISE YET...
WHATTYA SAY?
[DEMICAS] HHRGH...
(SHAKY EXHALE)
I KNOW FOR A FACT HE'D JUST
EMBARRASS YOU ALL OVER AGAIN.
I PICKED UP NEW RAID ITEMS,
IT WOULDN'T BE THE SAME FIGHT.
AND RELYING ON EQUIPMENT
IS EXACTLY WHY
YOU WOULDN'T WIN IN A REMATCH.
I'M GONNA CUT YOU
INTO PIECES?!
SO TELL ME WHICH ONE YOU PREFER:
HAMBURGER OR MINCED CUTLETS?
THEY'RE BOTH TASTY,
AS LONG AS I MARINADE THEM IN
SOME DEMI‐WHATEVER‐IT‐IS SAUCE.
URGH! YOU'RE GONNA HAVE A
HARD TIME RUNNING THAT MOUTH
WITHOUT ANY DAMN TEETH!
WELL THAT'S NOT VERY NICE,
MISTER DEMI‐DING‐DONG.
(GRUNTS)
(WILLIAM CHUCKLES)
YOU ARE REALLY STARTING
TO PISS ME OFF!
DON'T GET BENT OUT OF
SHAPE, DEMI‐DINGLEBERRY.
I'M GONNA RIP YOUR HEAD OFF!
(DOOR OPENS)
[TETORA] AND WOULDN'T YOU KNOW
IT, HALF THE GUYS IN BRIGANDIA
WENT TO THE GUILD‐HALL HERE
AND JUST BAILED ON HIM!
I CAN'T BLAME THEN REALLY.
SOME CAT PIRATE GUY,
WHO WASN'T EVEN IN A GUILD,
KICKED THEIR BUTTS.
AND ON TOP OF ALL THAT, THEIR
LEAD STRATEGIST, LONDARK,
WAS ONE OF THE FIRST
TO LEAVE AND GO WEST.
[NAOTSUGU]
OK, SO WHAT HAPPENED TO DEMICAS?
[TETORA] DEMI‐POO AND
WHAT'S LEFT OF BRIGANDIA
ARE ALL UNDERLINGS
OF SILVER SWORD NOW!
THAT'S HOW WE FINALLY GOT
A LITTLE CHANCE AT
PEACE IN SUSUKINO.
GUESS THAT MAKES SENSE.
OH YEAH! YOU HAVE GOT
TO MEET HIS WIFE.
SHE'S AN AWESOME LADY
ONCE YOU GET TO KNOW HER.
MARRIED?!
YOU'RE KIDDING!
I GUESS THERE'S HOPE FOR ME
IF HE CAN GET MARRIED.
AND HERE'S THE
REALLY AMAZING PART.
SHE'S THE DAUGHTER
OF AN ARISTOCRAT
AMONG THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND!
HE KIDNAPPED HER LOOKING
FOR A HOUSEKEEPER.
BUT POOR LITTLE
DEMI‐POO HERE
ENDED UP FALLING
IN LOVE WITH HER
AND HER HAMBURGERS
AND MINCED CUTLETS.
[NAOTSUGU]
THAT'S HILARIOUS!
[REGAN]
I'M SO JEALOUS!
(THE TRIO GIGGLES)
[SHIROE] EHEH...
THANKS TO HER, HE'S AS TAME
AS A HOUSE CAT NOWADAYS.
WHOA...HUH?
HEY, DEMI‐POO!
(SNARLS, WAR CRY)
(FRIGHTENED GASP)
(GROWL)
[TETORA]
WHY DID YOU STOP?
[DEMICAS] HUH... YOU'RE
PRETTY GOOD THERE, BUD
[NAOTSUGU] WE'RE INSIDE
A CITY, DILL WEED.
I KNOW YOU WON'T
TRY ANYTHING.
I COULD TAKE ON
THE GUARD, TOO.
ONE OF THESE DAYS, TETORA,
THAT LIP OF YOURS
IS GONNA MAKE ME FEED YOU
TO A GIANT, YOU LITTLE WENCH.
YOU'LL PROTECT
ME WON'T YOU?
PLEASE GO
SOMEWHERE ELSE!
[SHIROE] WHERE'D YOU FIND
YOUR NEW FRIEND?
FELL FROM THE SKY.
[WILLIAM] WELL THAT'S SOMETHING.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
WE'LL HAVE OUR 24 IF WE ADD
DEMICAS AND YOUR HEALER FRIEND.
YOU WANNA SETTLE THE SCORE
WITH SHIROE?
BURN OFF SOME OF THAT ENERGY
DURING THE RAID, BIG MAN.
[SHIROE] UH‐WAH
[DEMICAS] WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU HEARD ME, ARE YOU IN?!
[ALL]
YEAH!
[WILLIAM]
ALL RIGHT! GUESS WE'RE ALL HERE.
FIRST PARTY!
SECOND PARTY!
THIRD PARTY!
FOURTH PARTY!
LET'S MOVE OUT, PEOPLE!
(CHEERING)
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELVES
OUT THERE! MMHMMM.
[DEMICAS]
EAT THIS, YOU UGLY PUKES!
LIGHTNING... STRAIGHT! YAH!
(SHIROE SIGHS)
SOMEONE'S FEELING IT...
I WOULDN'T EXACTLY CALL THAT
"TEAMWORK," YOU KNOW.
[VOINEN] DON'T GET TOO FAR
AHEAD OF US, DEMICAS!
[DEMICAS]
TRY TO KEEP UP, FAT‐ASS!
[FEDERICO]
YEAH, YEAH. WHATEVER...
[VOINEN] WE'LL SEE HOW LONG
HE STICKS WITH US.
[NAOTSUGU]
I GUESS IT KINDA MAKES SENSE
FOR WILLIAM TO BE OUR COMMANDER.
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT
WE WERE ALL GONNA HAVE TO
FREAKIN' WALK HERE!
I CAN'T BE A SOARING STARLET
WITH BUNIONS ON MY TOOTSIES!
YEAH, YEAH.
[SHIROE] IT'S NOT LIKE EVERYONE
HERE HAS A GRIFFIN TO CALL ON.
BESIDES, I THINK WILLIAM HAS
A REASON FOR DOING IT THIS WAY.
HUH?
IF I WERE IN HIS POSITION,
I'D WANNA KNOW WHAT
EVERYONE IN THE PARTY CAN DO.
EVERY QUIRK, EVERY ABILITY.
OKAY, I GET IT, BUT DO YOU
THINK WE'RE GONNA EVEN
RESEMBLE A PARTY
ONCE WE GET THERE?
[SHIROE]
WELL... WE'LL SEE...
[TETORA]
UGH! I DON'T WANNA WALK ANYMORE!
GUESS THERE ONLY ONE OPTION...
I'LL JUST HAVE TO RIDE NAOTSUGU.
LISTEN, FLUFFHEAD,
I'M NOT YOUR DONKEY!
ACT ALL TOUGH IF YOU WANT...
BUT I KNOW YOU
REALLY LOVE ME. EHEE!
THE HELL I DO.
WUUGHHH!
HOW COULD YOU LIVE WITH
YOURSELF IF I ENDED UP
WITH A BLISTER ON
MY DELICATE STARLET TOES?
HEY!
THE ENTIRE TETORA FANBASE
WOULD BE IN MOURNING!
THE SUN WOULDN'T COME UP
FOR DAYS ON END!
[NAOTSUGU] TELL YA WHAT...
IF YOU GET DOWN ON YOUR
KNEES AND BEG ME...
MAYBE I'D HELP YOU OUT!
[TETORA]
I CANNOT BELIEVE YOU SAID THAT!
[NAOTSUGU] WOOOAAAH!
BUT IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
YOU NEVER TAKE A WARRIOR'S
SHIELD! GET BACK HERE!
[SHIROE] MPH...
[NAOTSUGU] COME HERE, DAMMIT!
[WILLIAM] YOUR TEAM
CERTAINLY SEEMS RELAXED.
WE TRY NOT TO TAKE
THINGS TOO SERIOUSLY.
HMPH...
I THINK I'M GETTING CLOSE
TO FIGURING OUT DEMICAS.
[SHIROE] I'D HOPE SO,
HE SEEMS PRETTY SIMPLE.
[WILLIAM] WELL WE ALREADY KNOW
HE'S NOT A STRANGER TO RAIDS.
I'LL FIGURE OUT THE BEST WAY
TO USE HIM IN A FIGHT
SOON ENOUGH... IF I CAN'T...
THEN PERHAPS I'M NOT THE
LEADER I THOUGHT I WAS.
STARE AT ME ALL YOU WANT...
BUT I'M GONNA BE PAYING YOU
BACK BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
[VOINEN] I HOPE WE GET THIS DONE
BEFORE NEW YEAR'S.
[NAOTSUGU]
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN...
WE'VE GOT A BUNCH OF THINGS
GOING ON AROUND THE HOLIDAYS.
DON'T WANNA MISS OUT...
[MARIELLE] I KNOW.
I JUST WISH THIS WHOLE THING
WASN'T SO HARD ON YOU...
[NAOTSUGU, VOICE CHAT]
I'M OKAY.
[MARIELLE]
YOU SURE YOU'RE ALL RIGHT?
ONE OF THOSE GUYS HAS
ME WORRIED, YOU KNOW?
DIDN'T THAT DINKY FACE
GUY RUN SUSUKINO?
[NAOTSUGU]
HIS NAME'S DEMICAS.
ITS NOT LIKE HE'S
A PROBLEM FOR ME.
WILLIAM STAYS ON HIS CASE,
SO THAT'S GOOD.
NOT TO MENTION HIS WIFE
IS SUPPOSEDLY IN CHARGE.
[MARIELLE, VOICE CHAT]
I'LL BET SHE IS.
THAT'S USUALLY HOW IT WORKS!
(DEMICAS GROWLS)
[NAOTSUGU] OKAY...
[MARIELLE] SO WHAT'S YOUR
FOOD LIKE OUT THERE?
DON'T TELL ME YOU'RE JUST
EATING THE SAME THING EVERY DAY.
I'M SURE YOU'RE CRAVING SOME
CHICKEN THIS TIME OF YEAR!
CHICKEN AND WINTER REALLY
DO GO HAND‐IN‐HAND!
IT'S CHICKEN SEASON!
[NAOTSUGU] UH... WHAT IS YOUR
DEAL WITH CHICKEN? WEIRD.
[MARIELLE]
CHICKEN IS GREAT!
IT'S CHOCK FULL OF
NUTRIENTS AND YUMMINESS!
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH, SURE...
I'M REALLY HOPING YOU CAN MAKE
IT BACK IN TIME FOR CHRISTMAS,
OKAY, NAOTSUGU?
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW HOW IT ITS...
I'LL DO WHAT I CAN
TO MAKE IT, ALL RIGHT?
LATER.
[MARIELLE]
YEAH, I'LL TALK TO YOU TOMORROW.
SAME TIME, 'KAY? HMPH.
(VOICE CHAT ENDING)
[HENRIETTA] MA‐RI‐ELLE!
[MARIELLE] EHHHH...
[HENRIETTA] SWEARING YOUR
ETERNAL LOVE OVER TELEPATHY?
[HENRIETTA] YOU TWO ARE LIKE
A VIDEO GAME SOAP OPERA!
[HENRIETTA] I SUPPOSE NEXT,
YOU'RE GONNA START
GETTING ON HIM FOR PUTTING IN
TOO MUCH TIME AT WORK.
YOU'RE LETTING YOUR IMAGINATION
RUN AWAY WITH YOU.
(SIGH) WE REALLY
NEED TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE THIS MINAMI SPY
COULD BE HIDING.
WE CAN'T LET IT SLIP BY US...
THAT'S WHY WE ESTABLISHED
STRICT PROTOCOLS
FOR CONTACTING THE OTHERS
IN THE FIRST PLACE!
YOU KNOW THAT.
I KNOW, OKAY?!
WE'RE BEING CAREFUL, HENRIETTA,
WE DECIDED TO LIMIT OUR CALLS TO
JUST ONCE A DAY AT NINE O'CLOCK.
OH? REALLY?!
TAKE IT EASY,
IT'S NOT THAT EITHER.
ANYWAY, I DON'T
KNOW WHERE HE IS,
AND IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE DISCUSSING
MILITARY STRATEGY
OR ANYTHING.
IT'S GOTTA BE OKAY...
ALL I KNOW IS HE'S GONNA BE
IN A BIG RAID, OR SOMETHING.
I'M NOT ASKING HIM ABOUT IT!
AND I KNOW ONE THING...
AFTER A BIG BATTLE, HE NEEDS
TO HAVE SOME DOWN TIME!
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M TRYING
TO MAKE HIM COME HOME!
AND WELL BESIDES,
I'M TECHNICALLY
SHIROE AND NAOTSUGU'S
DIRECT CONTACT
WITH THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE.
SO, WHAT I'M REALLY
DOING IS WORKING!
YOU'RE PUTTING OUR SECURITY AT
RISK BY ABUSING YOUR AUTHORITY!
SO CAN I?
PRETTY PLEASE?
WHAT IN THE WORLD AM I
GONNA DO WITH YOU, REALLY?
I CANNOT BE COMPLICIT
IN ALL OF THIS...
IT'S OKAY BY ME!
AH!
BESIDES I'M YOUR GUILD MASTER
SO YOU KINDA HAVE TO LET ME.
AH... HAHAHA HMMM
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU PUT IT
THAT WAY, HOW CAN I SAY NO?
(SIPS)
(MUNCH, CHEWS)
(CLOCK TICKING)
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI, I NEED YOU
TO STAY BEHIND IN THE CITY.
UH...
I'VE GOT A TASK FOR YOU TO DO
THAT ONLY YOU ARE
CAPABLE OF COMPLETING.
I NEED YOU TO PROTECT THE
PRINCESS WHILE I'M GONE.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
THERE ARE SPIES
SUSPECTED FROM MINAMI
IN THE CITY.
AND IF THEY'RE ACTUALLY HERE,
MY LORD BELIEVE THE
PRINCESS NEEDS PROTECTION.
I CAN UNDERSTAND
THAT, HOWEVER...
I'M GETTING THE FEELING
HE HAD ANOTHER REASON
TO LEAVE ME HERE IN AKIHABARA
[RAYNESHIA] PARDON ME...
[AKATSUKI] HM...?
WHAT IS THAT
YOU'RE EATING?
RED BEAN BUN.
RED BEAN BUN...?
AND WHAT KIND OF TEA IS THIS
THAT YOU'RE HAVING WITH IT?
[AKATSUKI]
ROASTED GREEN TEA.
SO I'M GUESSING APPLE TEA ISN'T
EXACTLY TO YOUR LIKING THEN?
RED BEAN BUNS AND ROASTED
GREEN TEA ALWAYS GO TOGETHER.
OKAY...
I DON'T GET IT...
EVERYTHING'S SO DIFFICULT.
HM...?
IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE
SINCE I CAME TO AKIHABARA,
AND THERE'S STILL A
LOT ABOUT YOUR CULTURE,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I GUESS, THERE'S A LOT
I NEED TO LEARN
ABOUT THE CUSTOMS
OF YOUR PEOPLE.
UH... MY PREFERENCES
AREN'T CUSTOM.
APPLE TEA IS NICE, TOO.
AKATSUKI, THANK YOU
FOR BEING SO KIND.
(ANNOYED GROAN)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
WHY DO I FEEL SO AWKWARD?
HMMMM...
[TATARA] GOOD MORNING.
[AKATSUKI] MPH...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
JUST ABOUT EVERY GAMER KNOWS
THAT YOU CAN ONLY GET POWERFUL
EPIC‐CLASS ITEMS IN RAIDS.
THAT'S HOW MY LORD
ACQUIRED HIS GRIFFIN.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT IS THE
PROOF THAT YOU AND YOUR PARTY
COMPLETED A LARGE
SCALE RAID OR EVENT.
ME, I DON'T HAVE ANY
RAIDING EXPERIENCE AT ALL.
ANOTHER WAY TO GET AN ITEM
OR WEAPON LIKE THAT
IS TO BUY ONE
FROM A VENDER.
BUT THAT CAN BE
VERY EXPENSIVE.
HOWEVER...
[TATARA]
IN CASE YOU WERE WONDERING,
THE PRICE IS NOT NEGOTIABLE.
I DON'T CARE TO HAGGLE.
(SIGH)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
NO WAY!
THAT'S MORE THAN TWICE
EVERYTHING I HAVE!
I MUST GET STRONGER!
[VOINEN] THIS IS IT. THE BOTTOM
OF THE DEPTHS OF PALM...
[FEDERICO] IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
I DIDN'T EVEN THINK IT WAS HERE!
JUST LOOK AT THE SIZE OF THOSE
DOORS, THEY'RE RIDICULOUS.
AND THIS IS THE
ENTRANCE, RIGHT?
[SHIROE]
IT IS.
[NAOTSUGU]
WE FINALLY MADE IT!
[DEMICAS, THINKING]
ALRIGHT, SHIROE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL
YOU'RE AFTER INSIDE THESE DOORS.
BUT I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T GET IT.
YOU'VE GOT A DREAM, LITTLE MAN.
AND I'M GONNA RIP IT TO SHREDS!
BY THE TIME I'M DONE WITH YOU,
YOU'RE GONNA BE CRYING FOR
SOMEONE TO GET YOU OUTTA HERE!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
SLUMBERING FAR BENEATH
THE DEPTHS OF PALM LIES
THE RAID ZONE ABYSSAL SHAFT.
THERE, THE FULL‐RAID
PARTY BEGINS.
IN A BATTLE OF OFFENSE
AND DEFENSE,
SHIROE, WILLIAM, AND DEMICAS END
UP FIGHTING NOT ONLY THE BATTLE,
BUT THEIR OWN FEELINGS AS WELL.
AND ANOTHER MUST FIGHT
HER OWN LONELINESS.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!