[NYANTA] I DOUBT THAT EVEN
SHIROE‐ECHHI COULD HAVE
ANTICIPATED A
PREDICAMENT LIKE THIS.
(SIGH) LOOKS LIKE I'M GONNA
NEED TO INTERVENE
A LITTLE MORE DIRECTLY
THAN I'D PLANNED.
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO DO IT RIGHT.
IF YOU'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A TOWN OR VILLAGE,
YOU NEED TO DO WHATEVER IT
TAKES TO GET THE CONFLICT
AWAY FROM THE POPULATION AS
QUICKLY AS YOU CAN.
I UNDERSTAND... IF YOU'RE
FIGHTING FOR YOUR HOME...
YOU WANT A HOME STANDING ONCE
THE FIGHTING'S DONE.
LEAVING THE STRUCTURES IN
TACT ONLY MAKES SENSE.
[SERARA] RIGHT! WE CAN'T
USE OUR TELEPATHIC LINK,
SO LEAVE YOUR PARTY‐CHAT ON
WHILE YOU GUYS GET OVER HERE!
ROGER THAT.
[MINORI, THINKING] NONE OF
THEM ARE ALL THAT POWERFUL.
IT'S JUST THAT THERE'S SO MANY!
WE'VE GOTTA DO SOMETHING!
[SERARA] YOU THINK MISS
ROE2'S OKAY BACK THERE?
[TOYA] C'MON! BIG SIS
CAN HANDLE HERSELF!
[MAN A] OVER HERE! HURRY!
(SERARA GASPS)
[MOTHER B] DON'T LET
GO OF MY HAND.
[MAN A] C'MON! KEEP MOVING!
[TOYA] SERARA? YOU OKAY?
IT'S AMAZING THEY'RE
ACTING SO CALM.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
[ALL] UH...?
[MINORI] IT'S THE
ODYSSEY KNIGHTS!
[TOYA] SO THEY'RE
GONNA FIGHT 'EM!
[SERARA] THAT'S WHY THE
VILLAGERS AREN'T PANICKING!
[TOYA] WE NEED TO KEEP MOVING.
HEH. (HEAVY BREATHS)
(KNOCK, KNOCK)
[RUDY] MISS ISUZU?
CAN I TALK TO YOU?
UH... (EXHALE)
MM?
UH... MM.
[ISUZU] DO YOU THINK... THAT
THE BATTLE'S ALREADY STARTED?
(EXHALES)
MISS ISUZU!
UH? WHAT NOW?
(GIGGLE)
THERE'S NO NEED TO FEAR!
RUNDELLHAUS KODE IS HERE!
SAPHIR VILLAGE
AND MISS ISUZU!
ALONG WITH MISS
MINORI AND SERARA!
YOU ARE SAFE WITH MY
PASSIONATE ORB OF LAVA
PROTECTING YOU FROM HARM! GAH!
RUDY! THIS IS NO TIME
TO GOOF AROUND! HM?
EHEHEHE...
MM?
PREPARE YOURSELF...
WHAT NOW, RUDY?
UH...? HUH?
WHA‐ WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
[RUDY] THIS IS CALLED
THE "BIRD SHOE."
YOU WON'T REALLY FLY LIKE
A BIRD OR ANYTHING PER SE.
BUT YOU WILL NOTICE BEING ABLE
TO GET AROUND MUCH MORE QUICKLY!
SO IT'S A SPELL TO
MAKE ME RUN FASTER?
EXACTLY.
OH! THIS IS AWESOME!
[RUDY] I TOLD YOU
I'M A GENIUS, RIGHT?!
EHEH! WHATEVER YOU
SAY RUDY. UH! HUH?
LET'S GO!
YEAH!
(RUNNING)
(FRIGHTENED)
(BATTLE CRIES)
WHAT IS THIS...?
(MORE BATTLE CRIES
AND CHUCKLING)
(MINORI INHALES)
[TOYA] THEY WANNA DIE...?
[KNIGHT A] COME AND GET ME,
COME AND GET ME!
[KNIGHT B] OVER HERE,
I'M RIGHT HERE!
[KNIGHT C] GET HIM!
OH NO... WHAT'RE
THEY DOING?
UWHAHH!
(LAUGHTER)
(WYVERN SNARLING)
[KNIGHT C] OVER HERE!
[KNIGHT D]
COME AND GET US! GET US!
(BATTLE CRIES)
[SHUNICHI]
ANCHOR HOWL!
[KNIGHT G]
SHUNICHI! YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
[KNIGHT D] LET ME DIE WITH YOU!
[KNIGHT C] ME, TOO!
(SCREAM)
THEY HAVE NO...
STRATEGY... OR TEAMWORK.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY'RE MAKING THE
WYVERNS ATTACK THEM!
I DON'T GET IT! WHAT ARE
THEY DOING OUT THERE?
[SHUNICHI]
I'M RIGHT HERE!
DO IT! TAKE ME TO THE
OTHER SIDE! ARGHHH!
[KNIGHT G]
UGHHH... EH?
[KNIGHT H]
UGH, WHAT, I'M BACK ALREADY.
[KNIGHT F] SO QUICK.
[KNIGHT G] THAT WAS
MY THIRD TIME.
[KNIGHT H]
GO, GO, GO!
[KNIGHT I]
AH! LET'S DO IT AGAIN!
[TOYA] I WAS RIGHT...
THEY REALLY WANNA DIE!
[ROE2] IT'S A PRETTY INTERESTING
STRATEGY IF YOU ASK ME.
[ROE 2] THE SHRINE
IS RESPAWNING THEM.
IT'S JUST LIKE A CATHEDRAL.
ONLY THEY DON'T HAVE TO ENDURE
THE WAIT TIME THEY
USUALLY WOULD.
(KNIGHT GRUNTING)
WHAT KIND OF INVENTOR COULD
COME UP WITH THAT...?
IT'S REALLY IMPRESSIVE.
BIG SIS ROE2?
YOU'VE GOTTA BE
INTERESTED, RIGHT, TOYA?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
"INTERESTED?!" THAT MACHINE
IS DISGUSTING...!
TOTALLY WRONG!
NO... THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH IT.
IT'S JUST AN INVENTION
THAT USES THE LAWS
OF THIS WORLD.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT!
[ROE2]
AND FROM WHERE I'M STANDING...
THOSE KNIGHTS ARE GIVING
UP THEIR EMPATHIUM
TO THE SYSTEM FREELY ENOUGH.
[SERARA] EH?
THE HARVESTING RATE IS EXCELLENT
CONSIDERING ALL THE
DYING THEY'RE DOING.
THE GENIUSES ARE DEFINITELY
BENEFITTING FROM IT.
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?!
THEY'RE ALL DYING...!
WE GOTTA STOP THIS!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO.
IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE TRYING
TO DIE OUT THERE.
[ROE2] NONE OF THEM
ARE SLOWING DOWN
OR STOPPING.
THEIR ACCELERATED TRIP THROUGH
THE SHRINE LET'S THEM
SEE THEIR FORMER LIVES,
AND THEY'RE ADDICTED TO IT!
OF COURSE, I NEVER
EXPERIENCED IT MYSELF.
(MECHANICAL WHIRLING)
LONDARK HERE, NO HOSTILE
CONTACTS HAVE BEEN SEEN.
THE MAGIC RAILS APPEAR TO
BE RUNNING SPLENDIDLY.
[SORCERER B] WE'VE RECEIVED
A REPORT FROM LORD LONDARK.
EVERYTHING APPEARS TO BE WELL.
[MIZPHA] HE SCRAMBLES OUT OF
SUSUKINO LIKED A WHIPPED DOG,
AND STILL GETS
TREATED LIKE NOBILITY
BECAUSE HE'S AN ADVENTURER?!
[SORCERER A] ACCORDING TO THE
NIGHTSHADE SERVANT
ON RECONNAISSANCE,
THE ODYSSEY KNIGHTS HAVE
ENGAGED
A FLIGHT OF WYVERNS IN SAPHIR
VILLAGE. (GULPS AND SLURPS)
HEH! LET THE FOOLS DIE.
RELEASE THE SERVANTS,
HALF OF THEM!
[SORCERER C]
YES, MA'AM!
[SORCERER D]
CONDITIONS ARE CURRENTLY STABLE.
[SORCERER C]
EXCELLENT. COMMENCE ACTIVATION.
[SORCERER D] SYNCHRONIZE BED 20
WITH THE SYSTEM. MONITOR EXP.
[SORCERER C]
PARTY CHAT ENGAGED.
[NAKARUNARD] YOU KIDDING ME? YOU
ACTUALLY MADE THIS THING WORK?!
[ZELDEUS] YES, IT'S ABLE TO
SUMMON A NIGHTSHADE SERVANT.
THE PERSON OF THE LAND'S
MIND IS PROJECTED ON IT.
[MIZPHA] AND IF I'M NOT
MISTAKEN THE EXPERIENCE POINTS
FROM THE SERVANT LEVELS UP
THE PERSON OF THE LAND.
[NAKARUNARD]
NO WAY.
[ZELDEUS]
THE BEST PART IS...
IF THE SERVANT
PERISHES IN BATTLE,
THE PERSON OF THE LAND
CONTROLLING IT STAYS SAFE.
[JARED]
TEE‐HEE! IN A WAY,
WE'RE ESSENTIALLY GIVING THESE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
TEMPORARY "IMMORTALITY."
(LAUGHTER)
[KUONG] GOD, YOU'RE CREEPY!
[JARED] ACK! KEEP IT
DOWN WHILE THE GROWN‐UPS
ARE TALKING BUSINESS!
[KUONG] OW, THAT HURTS!
[ZELDEUS] ENOUGH YOU TWO!
[KUONG] KNOCK IT OFF!
[KAZUHIKO] SO IT'S BASICALLY
A POWER‐UP TECHNIQUE?
[NAKARUNARD] A FAST
POWER‐UP TECHNIQUE!
[JARED] OH THIS IS FUN!
[KUONG] MAYBE FOR YOU!
[MIZPHA] FASCINATING.
[JARED] ONCE PERFECTED,
WE'LL HAVE AS MANY LAND PEOPLE
IN OUR ARMY AS WE NEED!
[KUONG] COME ON, ENOUGH ALREADY!
(JARED CREEPILY LAUGHING)
[SORCERER C] ACKNOWLEDGED.
I WILL BEGIN ADMINISTERING
THE EXPERIENCE POTION
IN TEN MINUTES.
HUH? NO DON'T! IT'S DANGEROUS!
[SORCERER B] GENERAL MIZPHA,
SIR KAZUHIKO INSISTS WE REFRAIN
FROM ADMINISTERING THE POTIONS.
[MIZPHA] I'M SURE HE DOES,
HE'S A HYPOCRITE.
THE MAN'S AN ADVENTURER, AND
WE ARE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
IMMORTALS HAVE NO STAKE
WHATSOEVER IN OUR WAR.
WE ARE THE ONES WHO
TRULY MAKE SACRIFICES.
[KNIGHTS] UGH...
[MIZPHA] ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
[KNIGHT H] OHH...
[ROE2] TRUTH BE TOLD, I
DON'T FULLY UNDERSTAND
THE SOCIETY YOU'RE DEVELOPING.
IT SEEMS QUITE
INEFFICIENT TO ME.
[KNIGHT L] WHAT'RE THEY DOING?!
[TOYA] HUH?
[SHUNICHI] NIGHTSHADE SERVANTS?
[MABANJIN] WHERE THE HELL
DID THEY COME FROM?!
[SHUNICHI] NO! PROTECT THE
SHRINE AT ALL COSTS!
[KNIGHTS] YEAH!
[ROE2] YOU JUST HAVE
TO REMEMBER THAT
THE WORLD YOU DON'T SEE
IS BIGGER THAN THE
WORLD YOU DO SEE...
(DEATH CRIES) (BATTLE EXERTS)
[ROE2] OUR REALM
OF UNDERSTANDING
IS INCREDIBLY SMALL
AND INCONSEQUENTIAL...
SO THE FACT THAT I CAN'T
WRAP MY HEAD AROUND
ANY OF THIS ISN'T SURPRISING.
[TOYA] UNGH!
[MINORI] TOYA!
[SERARA] TOYA...! WAIT...
YOU NEED A HEALER!
GO, WOLFY!
(SQUEE)
[WOLF‐CHAN] YIP‐YIP!
(SERARA GASPS)
[SERARA] LOOKS LIKE SOME
OF THE PEOPLE HERE DIDN'T
GET TO THE SHELTER IN TIME!
LET'S GO HELP 'EM, WOLFY!
[WOLF‐CHAN]
YIP‐YIP‐YIP!
(WAR CRY)
[TOYA]
WHIRLWIND SLASH!
JOIN THE FIGHT...
TOYA ALREADY HAS.
HUH?
(EXHALE)
JUST WHO ARE YOU
ANYWAY ROE2?
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
(BREATH) (HALF LAUGH)
[ROE2] HEH, THIS IS THE SECOND
TIME YOU'VE ASKED ME THAT.
(BREATH)
[BOTH] UH? ACK!
[ISUZU] HYAHH!
[RUDY] HAHHHH!
OH...?
WHAT'S THAT?
[ISUZU] WHAT WERE
THOSE THINGS ANYWAY?
THEY JUST POPPED RIGHT UP!
AND I DIDN'T SEE ANY YIN
DISPERSAL WHEN WE BEAT THEM.
(EXHALE) HEY, MISS ISUZU...
ARE YOU OKAY OVER THERE?
YOU'RE NOT WEARING
YOURSELF OUT ARE YOU?
[ISUZU] HMPH...? NO, I'M FINE...
YOU READY FOR MORE?
YOU SHOULD BE BETTER
IN ABOUT A MINUTE!
[WOLF‐CHAN] YIP‐YIP!
[SERARA] HUH?
GIMME A SECOND OKAY, WOLFY?
I GOTTA HEAL THIS GUY!
[SHUNICHI] ALL RIGHT EVERYONE!
FALL BACK TO THE CITY LIMITS!
[SHUNICHI] NIGHTSHADE SERVANTS
ARE RALLYING AGAINST US!
DO NOT LET THEM LIVE!
AND GET THE WYVERNS
ON THE GROUND!
HAVE THEM FOLLOW YOU INTO
ONE OF THE STRUCTURES
WHERE THEY CAN'T
MOVE! THEN STRIKE!
[SHUNICHI] GET 'EM ALL! DON'T
LET ANY OF THEM ESCAPE!
KILL THEM! KILL THEM ALL! AND
THEN DO SOME DYING YOURSELVES!
[TOYA] GUH. (SHARP INHALE)
(KNIGHTS CHEERING)
[TOYA]
HEY...
HEY!
(PUNCH)
(GASP)
TOYA?
HUH? WAS THAT TOYA?
HUH?
TOYA!
[TOYA]
HEY! (PUNCH)
[SHUNICHI]
HUH?
WHAT THE HECK IS
YOUR PROBLEM?!
STAY OUT OF THIS, BOY.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS HAD A JOB...
EVERYONE IN THE ODYSSEY
KNIGHTS IS SUPPOSED TO BE
PROTECTING THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND!
BUT YOU'RE GOING TO
DESTROY THEIR CITY!
[TOYA]
PEOPLE LIVE IN THOSE BUILDINGS!
THAT...
DOESN'T CONCERN ME...
WHAT! ARE YOU LISTENING
TO YOURSELF?!
THERE'S GOTTA BE ANOTHER WAY
FOR YOUR GUYS TO DO THIS!
IF YOU WANT TO BE CRAZY AND
KILL YOURSELF, GO FOR IT.
BUT C'MON... YOU
DON'T HAVE TO DESTROY
A BUNCH OF PEOPLE'S
LIVES IN THE PROCESS!
[SHUNICHI] YOU COULDN'T
POSSIBLY UNDERSTAND, KID.
(GASP)
(GROWLING)
WHY ARE YOU SO WORRIED
ABOUT US ANYWAYS.
YOU DO KNOW WE CAN'T
DIE HERE, RIGHT?
WE COULDN'T EVEN COMMIT
SUICIDE IF WE WANTED TO.
YEAH, BUT...
LOOK!
WE JUST WANNA
GET OUTTA HERE!
WE ARE GOING TO
GET BACK HOME!
UH...!
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND.
WHEN WE RESPAWN, WE GET
TO SEE OUR FAMILIES!
YOU GET TO SEE THE WORLD WE
LEFT BEHIND EVERY SINGLE TIME.
EVEN IF JUST FOR A MOMENT!
IT'S PROOF THEY MUST BE
CONNECTED IN SOME WAY.
[SHUNICHI] IT'S PROOF!
(TOYA GASPS)
[SHUNICHI]
I'LL DIE... AND I'LL DIE!
AND I'LL KEEP ON DYING AS
MANY TIMES AS IT TAKES!
NO ONE CAN STOP ME FROM
GOING BACK TO OUR WORLD!
THIS ISN'T THE WAY...
I WAS... I WAS SUPPOSED TO
GET MARRIED THIS SUMMER.
AND... AND I WAS GONNA GIVE
UP THIS STUPID GAME FOR GOOD!
I MEAN, WE WENT APARTMENT
SHOPPING AND EVERYTHING.
I'M GETTING MARRIED! I LOVE HER!
I CAN'T BE STUCK HERE PLAYING
THIS STUPID THING FOREVER!
WHEN MY LEASE IS DONE,
I'M PACKING UP AND GETTING A
NEW PLACE WITH MY WIFE!
SHE'S REALLY BEEN
PUTTING ON THE PRESSURE.
SHE TELLS ME
EVERYTIME I SEE HER,
SHE WANTS OUT OF HER FOLKS'
HOUSE LIKE, YESTERDAY!
"FINE BABY, JUST GIMME SOME
TIME, AND I'LL MAKE IT HAPPEN!"
SHE CAN'T HANDLE IT ANYMORE.
I'VE GOTTA GET HER OUT!
COME ON, KID!
DON'T YOU HAVE SOMEONE BACK
HOME? DON'T DENY IT!
[TOYA] ALL I KNOW IS THAT
THERE'RE PEOPLE IN MY LIFE HERE
WHO ARE IMPORTANT TO ME.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU THINK...
THIS WORLD IS REAL!
[SHUNICHI] SHUT UP!
[TOYA] UWAH!
[SHUNICHI] YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING! [TOYA] AHHHH!
(WATER SPLASHING)
[TOYA] AHNGH!
[SHUNICHI] THIS PLACE HAS
NOTHING! NOT EVEN DEATH!
WE'RE NOT IN SOME FANTASY LAND!
WE'RE NOT EVEN IN
HELL! YOU GET IT!
THIS PLACE DOESN'T EVEN EXIST!
(DISAPPOINTED)
AND THE ONLY THING
KEEPING US HERE
ARE VERMIN LIKE YOU
CLINGING TO LIFE.
YOU REFUSE TO LET IT END.
THE REST OF US ARE LEFT HERE TO
SUFFER. AND BEG FOR ESCAPE!
[TOYA]
(GRUNT AND GROANING) UGH...
THERE'S MORE TO IT THAN
THAT, AND YOU KNOW IT.
YOU HAVE GOT TO BE
ABLE TO SEE THAT!
TOYA...
[TOYA] YOU'VE GOTTA
BE ABLE TO SEE
WHAT'S RIGHT IN
FRONT OF YOU!
(CAR SCREECHING AND CRASHING)
[MAN A] HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
[MAN B] HELLO?! THERE'S
BEEN AN ACCIDENT!
(MUTTERING)
[MINORI] TOYA... IT'S
ME... IT'S MINORI!
[TOYA] MISTER. LIFE...
IS WHAT YOU MAKE OF IT.
YOU CAN BE ALIVE,
BUT DEAD INSIDE...
EVEN BACK IN OUR OLD WORLD.
SURE YOU CAN WALK AROUND
AND LIVE YOUR LIFE...
BUT IT'S MEANINGLESS IF
YOU DON'T CARE ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW IT TRUE!
[SHUNICHI]
HEH! TELL YA WHAT, KID.
IF YOU'VE GOT A PROBLEM WITH ME,
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD TAKE IT
UP WITH THE SYSTEM OPERATOR.
THEN THEY CAN BOOT ME FROM THE
SERVER. AND THEN I'LL BE FREE!
OKAY... I KNOW
HOW HE FEELS...
I GET THAT HE WANTS TO GO
HOME AND ALL... BUT STILL.
MISS ISUZU...
OH...!
THE GUY OUT THERE.
I UNDERSTAND WHAT HE MEANT.
AH...
UGN. HE ISN'T RIGHT.
[ISUZU] EVERYONE... EVERYONE...
THEY'RE ALL REAL. HMM.
[MINORI, THINKING]
TOYA WAS ALWAYS SMILING
EVEN THOUGH HE WAS STUCK
IN THAT WHEELCHAIR.
MAYBE IT WAS BECAUSE
HE UNDERSTOOD
THAT THE WORLD AROUND
HIM CHANGED,
AND THERE WAS NOTHING HE
COULD DO ABOUT IT ANYMORE.
THE WORLD GOT SO
BIG AND UNFAIR.
AND THERE WASN'T ANY
HOPE TO FIGHT AGAINST IT.
HE KEPT GOING, AND DOING WHAT
HE COULD WITH THAT HE HAD.
HE ACCEPTED HIS FATE!
(SNARL)
[SHUNICHI] HUAH!
[SHUNICHI] UWAH!
[TOYA] UGH!
[MINORI, THINKING] AND HE'S
DOING THE SAME THING NOW!
[ROE2] SO TOYA IS
PROTESTING FATE.
SERARA IS CASTING
HEARTBEAT HEALING ON ALL
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND AFTER
SHE DRESSES THEIR WOUNDS.
ISUZU AND RUNDELLHAUS ARE
DEFENDING THE VILLAGERS
AS THEY'RE MAKING
THEIR WAY HERE.
(BATTLE EXERTS)
[ROE2] THE THING IS, THOUGH,
AS HARD AS THEY'RE FIGHTING.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
(BATTLE EXERTS)
CONSIDERING EVERYTHING
THAT'S GOING ON...
YOU ALREADY KNOW THE
ANSWER, DON'T YOU?
UH?
[ROE2] I MEAN I
COULD STAND HERE AND
ASK YOU THE SAME
QUESTIONS, COULDN'T I?
WHERE DID YOU COME FROM?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[ISUZU] SOMETHING'S BEEN ON
MY MIND EVER SINCE YESTERDAY.
UH...?
[ISUZU] I'VE BEEN
THINKING AND THINKING.
BUT I DIDN'T REALLY FIGURE
IT ALL OUT UNTIL JUST NOW.
I HAD TO FIGHT MY
OWN INSECURITIES...
I JUST COULDN'T FIND
MY INSPIRATION.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
BUT YOU KNOW...?
I REALLY DID HAVE
IT GOOD BEFORE.
I HAD A GREAT DAD, WHO
LOVED ME AND CARED FOR ME.
AND WELL, LIFE
WAS FULL OF MUSIC!
WHEN I WAS SAD OR UPSET,
THERE WERE SO MANY
DIFFERENT TYPES OF SONGS
I COULD LISTEN TO.
MUSIC ALWAYS HELPED ME
THROUGH, NO MATTER WHAT.
BUT THIS...
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
42 SONGS ISN'T ENOUGH...
NOT AT ALL!
IT'S JUST AWFUL
THAT YOU CAN'T SING
WHENEVER YOU'RE SAD,
WHENEVER YOU'RE HAPPY.
MISS ISUZU...
WHICH IS WHY...
(LUTE STRUMMING)
UH...! WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
LET'S GO, RUDY!
UH! WHERE ARE WE GOING?!
[RUDY] SO UH...
WHAT'RE WE GONNA DO?
[ISUZU] WE'RE GOING TO PICK A
FIGHT! [RUDY] A FIGHT?!
[ISUZU] WE'RE GOING OUT
THERE TO PICK A FIGHT
WITH THE GODS WHO ONLY CREATED
42 SONGS FOR THIS WORLD.
AND I'M NOT GOING TO STOP UNTIL
THEY START SINGING ALONG.
[RUDY] (HEAVY BREATHING)
DON'T GO WITHOUT ME, MISS ISUZU!
[MINORI, THINKING] THERE'S
SOMETHING DIFFERENT ABOUT HER.
BUT I'M...
I'M NOT SURE IF
I REALLY WANT
TO KNOW WHAT IT IS.
NO, THAT SHOULDN'T
CHANGE ANYTHING.
NO MATTER WHO SHE IS, SHE IS
HERE WITH ME. AND MY FRIEND.
AND IN THE END.
THAT'S ALL I CAN ASK.
I MEAN, WHO AM I, REALLY?
WHERE AM I GOING?
SHE MAKES ME ASK...
... WHAT DO I WANT TO BE?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
UH?
[MINORI, THINKING] ISUZU?
SHE'S SINGING...!
THAT'S HER DREAM.
THAT'S WHAT SHE DOES.
YEAH, AND I HAVE A DREAM TOO...
I WANT TO BE LIKE SHIROE.
YES. THAT'S IT. I WANT
TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
I WANT TO CARVE NEW PATHS.
(INHALES) (SLAPS)
I AM THE APPRENTICE
OF MASTER SHIROE.
AND YOU'RE OUR BIG SISTER, ROE2!
[ROE2] UH?
YOU CAME FROM NOWHERE,
AND YOU'LL BE GOING BACK
THERE, BUT FOR RIGHT NOW...
YOU'RE WITH US, AND
YOU'RE OUR FRIEND!
(LAUGHING)
SO YOU FOUND YOUR ANSWER,
IN THE MIDDLE OF BATTLE?
THAT'S RIGHT I DID...
I HAVE FOUND MY ANSWER.
EVEN IF WE CAN'T CHANGE
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE CAN ALWAYS MAKE A DIFFERENCE
IF WE'RE WILLING TO TRY.
OKAY, SO SHOULDN'T YOU BE
OUT THERE HELPING TOYA?
MY BROTHER WILL BE JUST FINE.
YEAH, BUT HE CAN'T HEAR
A WORD YOU'RE SAYING.
RIGHT NOW, I HAVE
OTHER THINGS TO DO.
HM...
WELL IF YOU'D LIKED ME TO
HELP, I'M HERE FOR YOU.
SURE.
(MUSIC ENDING)
OKAY! YOU GOT IT, MINORI!
LET'S DO THIS! AFTER ALL,
WHAT'RE BIG SISTERS FOR?!
RIGHT!
SUMMON!
BEING A TRAVELER DOES COME
WITH CERTAIN RESPONSIBILITIES.
MINORI, DO YOU KNOW WHAT A
SHAME IT'D BE IF I SAID NO
TO YOU RIGHT NOW? ESPECIALLY
AFTER YOU ASKED ME SO NICELY!
ANYTIME MY LITTLE
SISTER NEEDS ME,
I'M GONNA BE THERE!
(FIGHTING)
[ROE2] THE STABILITY OF THE
CONVERGING FACTORS DIRECTLY
CORRELATES WITH THE INCREASING
SCALE OF THE BATTLE.
HOWEVER, THIS LEADS
TO RANK DETERMINISM.
SMALL FRAGMENTS ARE
UNNECESSARILY LOST
DURING THE COURSE OF THE EVENT.
NOT THAT THERE'S ANYTHING
WRONG WITH THAT...
EVERYBODY WANTS TO BE
HAPPY, IT'S NORMAL.
BUT, THINK ABOUT IT!
ALL THOSE DESIRES ARE LEADING
EVERYONE TO IMMENSE SORROWS.
DID I LOSE YOU?
MM‐HM.
WELL IT'S YOUR LANGUAGE;
I'M STILL TRYING TO LEARN IT!
IF YOU DON'T MIND MY SAYING SO
YOUR LANGUAGE IS THE ONLY THING
KEEPING ME FROM EXPRESSING
MY CONCLUSIONS PROPERLY.
CAN YOU REALLY ENDURE THIS
UNREASONABLE SOLITUDE WHILE
LIVING LIKE YOU'RE STUCK
IN A STONE AGE?
I KNOW IT'S TOO MUCH FOR ME!
BUT YOUR COMPASSION,
WHAT I CALL EMPATHIUM,
IT MAKES YOU CARE FOR
PEOPLE, AM I RIGHT?
[MINORI] HUH?
[LONDARK, VOICE CHAT] GENERAL
CONQUEROR OF THE EAST,
YOUR SERVANTS ARE UNDER
ATTACK AT THIS VERY MOMENT.
[MIZPHA] EXCUSE ME?!
[MIZPHA] WHO IS IT?!
[LONDARK] WELL WHO
DO WE HAVE HERE?
I FEEL LIKE WE'VE DONE
THIS BEFORE, HAVE WE NOT?
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
LONDARK STANDS IN DEFIANCE.
THE FEELINGS HE HAS FOR THIS
WORLD
HAVE GROWN WARPED AND TWISTED.
HE WONDERS WHY EVERYONE WAS
BROUGHT TO THIS WORLD
AND WHY NO ONE WAS
GIVEN A CHOICE.
NYANTA HAS NO ANSWERS.
TOYA, ISUZU, AND THE OTHER
JUNIOR MEMBERS
CONTINUE THEIR STRUGGLE.
AS THEY SEEK TO FIND
THEIR OWN ANSWERS.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES ARE
ALWAYS BESIDE ME.