[ROE2, VOICEOVER] I WASN'T
SURE HOW TO BEGIN THIS LETTER,
BUT I THINK THE MOST APPROPRIATE
WAY WOULD BE TO USE THE WORD,
"HELLO." SO...
HELLO, WORLD.
HELLO, SHIROE.
"SHIROE OF LOG HORIZON."
I MUST ADMIT, HEARING THAT NAME
TOOK ME A BIT OFF GUARD.
THE REASON IS BECAUSE I HAVE
A FEW OF YOUR MEMORIES
IN MY HEAD... SO I
FEEL A CONNECTION.
JUST LIKE YOU AND YOUR
FRIENDS ARE BEINGS
WHO CAME TO THIS WORLD
FROM A FARAWAY PLACE,
MY FAMILIARS AND I ARE ALSO
BEINGS FROM A DISTANT LAND.
MY NAME IS ROE2.
I AM ONE OF A GROUP THAT HAS
BECOME KNOWN AS "TRAVELLERS."
AND, MY CURRENT
JUXTAPOSITION IN THIS BODY,
MAKES ME SOMETHING AKIN
TO YOUR YOUNGER SISTER.
[SERARA] AAH! WHAT ARE WE
DOING IN THE KITCHEN TODAY...
I'M SO EXCITED?!
WELL LET ME SEE NOW... HMM?
[SERARA] OH?
[SOJIRO] THANKS FOR
COMING, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] ALRIGHT, JUST
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED...
... AND ABOUT THIS
NEW KIND OF BEING.
[SOJIRO] AND WELL,
THAT'S ABOUT IT...
[SHIROE] HMM... THE MARRIAGE
GENIUS, KAMAISARU, YOU SAY?
[NAZNA] IF YOU ASK
ME, IT'S MORE LIKE
HE'S PLAYIN' ALL THESE GIRLS.
[SHIROE] SO THE
WEST WIND GIRLS ARE
ACTUALLY THE ONES WHO FOUND HIM?
[NAZNA] YOU KNOW THAT'S RIGHT.
[AKATSUKI] MMM!
WE HAVE A LARGE
INTELLIGENCE NETWORK
MADE UP OF NOTHING
BUT LADIES, SHIROE.
[NAZNA] HEH HEH.
[SOJIRO] HMM...
YEP...! THEY'RE PRETTY
AMAZING, MY LORD.
YOU KNOW ABOUT IT, AKATSUKI?
NO, I KNOW NOTHING.
HUH?
[SHIROE]
UH...
SO WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?
[NAZNA]
HE'S SWITCHING MODES.
[SOJIRO]
I'LL FINISH THIS QUICKLY.
[KAMAISARU] PROVIDE ME WITH
WHAT I NEED, ADVENTURERS.
[SOJIRO] NAZNA!
[NAZNA] GOT IT! THERE!
[KAMAISARU]
WON'T YOU MARRY ME, MY DEAR?
[SOJIRO]
SINGLE STROKE SLASH!
YAHHH!
SO YOU JUST JUMPED IN
AND ATTACKED, HUH?
[NAZNA] YOU MESS WITH SOMEONE
IN WEST WIND BRIGADE,
YOU'RE GONNA PAY
THE PRICE FOR IT!
[AKATSUKI] WE WILL SHOW NO MERCY
WHEN IT COMES TO THAT, MY LORD.
[SHIROE] YOU HELPED
OUT, TOO, AKATSUKI?
NOPE. NO, I DIDN'T.
[SHIROE] HUH?
(HALF‐LAUGH)
SO? HOW DO WE GO ABOUT
CLASSIFYING THIS GUY?
[SOJIRO]
IS HE AN ENEMY?
"ENEMY," WELL?
IF THEY'RE GOING OUT OF THEIR
WAY TO START A FIGHT...
THEN WE MUST DEFEND OURSELVES.
[NAZNA]
AND THAT MEANS DOING WHATEVER
IT TAKES TO PROTECT THE CITY.
[SOJIRO]
DON'T WORRY, LEAVE IT TO US.
[AKATSUKI]
WE WILL HANDLE THIS, MY LORD.
[SHIROE] UH... OKAY, THANKS.
[NAZNA] UH‐HUH...
[SOJIRO]
COME TO THINK OF IT,
THIS GUY WAS RATHER UNUSUAL.
[SHIROE] "UNUSUAL"?
I MEAN FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE WE CAME HERE,
IT REALLY FELT LIKE THE GAME.
[NAZNA] YEAH. IT NEVER SEEMED
LIKE THERE WAS ANY REAL DANGER.
[SOJIRO] IT WAS LIKE
IT WASN'T REAL.
IT DIDN'T FEEL NORMAL,
LIKE WE FOUGHT THE GUY
ONSCREEN OR SOMETHING.
[SHIROE]
HMM.
[SARGE] DEEP FRIED
ROCKFISH IS THE BEST!
[SOLDIERS] DEEP FRIED ROCKFISH
IS THE BEST! (PANTING)
[ITHERUS] MASTER
ISAAC! MASTER ISAAC!
(ISAAC GRUNTING)
HOW DOES A MAN THAT BIG
MANAGE TO JUMP SO HIGH?
WHOA! TELL ME HOW HE
DOES IT, MASTER ISAAC!
JUST CALL ME ISAAC.
OH? OKAY.
WHO'RE YOU AGAIN?
I'M ITHERUS, SIR.
[ISAAC] OKAY, ITHERUS.
CAN YOU KEEP IT DOWN?
I'M TRYING TO GET SOME SLEEP
OVER HERE. (FIGHTING PRACTICE)
[ITHERUS] BUT, MASTER ISAAC,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE TRAINING
ALL MAIHAMA'S KNIGHTS
AND MAKING THEM BETTER.
[SOLDIERS] HYAHHHH!!
(STRUGGLING)
[ISAAC] DON'T BOTHER ME
WITH THE DETAILS, KID.
[ITHERUS] ALSO, I HEARD THAT MY
OLDER SISTER PRINCESS RAYNESHIA
IS CURRENTLY UNDER YOUR WATCH
INSIDE THE CITY LIMITS.
[ISAAC] YEAH, WELL
YA HEARD WRONG.
THAT'S NOT MY
JOB... GOT IT.
HER KEEPER'S ON LEAVE, I GUESS.
[ITHERUS] AND I TAKE IT HE'S
AN ADVENTURER TOO,
RIGHT? MASTER ISAAC, SIR?
[ISAAC] (SIGH) JUST ISAAC....
[REZARICK] MR. ISAAC.
[ISAAC] ERK!
WE SHOULD PROBABLY GIVE
THE MEN A LITTLE BREAK...
[ISAAC] WOULD YOU GUYS KNOCK IT
OFF WITH THE "MISTER" CRAP!?
[REZARICK] YOU HEAR THAT,
ITHERUS?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE SO
FORMAL WITH MR. ISAAC.
[ITHERUS] SO IT SHOULD
BE "MISTER ISAAC."
[ISAAC] ONE OF YOU IS ABOUT
TO GET PUNCHED IN THE FACE!
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH
THAT, MISTER ISAAC, SIR?
IT SOUNDS SO DASHING AND
DIGNIFIED, MISTER ISAAC!
(GIGGLING) [MAID B] I THINK
HE'S GOING TO EXPLODE!
[ISAAC] AHHH! YOU'RE
JUST BEGGIN' ME
TO INTRODUCE YOU TO THE
BLACK SWORD OF PAIN!
[MICHITAKA] WHEN
WE FIRST MET HIM,
HE LOOKED LIKE A NORMAL
PERSON OF THE LAND.
AND HE TOLD US HE HAD THE
ABILITY TO APPRAISE MINERALS.
EVER SINCE THE APOCALYPSE, WE
MADE IT A POINT TO DETERMINE
THE PRICE OF MATERIAL ITEMS BY
THEIR QUALITY OR WORKMANSHIP.
ADVENTURERS FLOCKED
FROM ALL AROUND
TO GET THINGS
VALUED FROM HIM.
BUT HERE'S THE DEAL...
LET'S SAY THIS NEW FRIEND OF
OURS APPRAISES JUST ANY OLD ROCK
AND SAYS IT HAS
GEMSTONE QUALITY.
NOW, I DON'T GET IT, BUT ALL OF
A SUDDEN EVERYBODY WOULD START
THINKING THAT THIS ROCK WAS A
24 CARAT DIAMOND OR SOMETHING.
[RODERICK] IN SHORT, THIS MAN
IS A MONSTER
OF SOME KIND WHO DEVALUES
ALL OF OUR KNOWN MEASUREMENTS
AND MATERIAL VALUES.
EVEN LENGTHS AND WEIGHTS
ARE SUSPECT NOW.
HE'S BUGRITH, THE
GENIUS OF MEASUREMENT.
A CONSISTENT STANDARD OF
MEASURES AND VALUES IS
MORE IMPORTANT THAN
YOU MIGHT THINK.
WE DID SOME SNOOPING,
AND WE ENDED UP
FINDING HIS HIDEOUT.
WE IMPROVISED A RAID TEAM.
BUT RAN INTO A SURPRISE.
[BUGRITH] (CHUCKLING)
WELL, WELL, WELL.
THIS SHOULD MAKE FOR
A NICE HAUL OF EMPATHIUM.
[MICHITAKA]
LIGHTNING STRAIGHT! HUH?
THIS GUY WAS A FLAT OUT
TRICKSTER!
NONE OF US KNEW HE COULD CONTROL
DISTANCES,
SPEEDS, TARGETING
AND SKILL DAMAGE
IN THE MIDDLE OF A BATTLE.
WE WERE SCREWED.
[BUGRITH] GIVE UP
YOUR EMPATHIUM, NOW,
OR SUFFER THE CONSEQUENCES!
[RODERICK] AND, JUST WHEN
EVERYONE WAS ABOUT TO GIVE UP...
[RODERICK] SORRY
I MADE YOU WAIT!
[RODERICK] THANKS TO HELP
FROM THE KUNIE TRIBE,
OUR SECRET WEAPON'S
COMPLETE AND READY TO GO!
[MICHITAKA]
NOW WE'RE TALKIN'!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, BUGRITH!
YOUR EVIL DEEDS ARE ABOUT
TO BE FOILED, MY FRIEND!
WITH THIS...! THE METRO BLADE!
[SHIROE] "METRO BLADE"?
[MARIELLE] YEAH, BUT ISN'T
THAT... JUST A RULER?
TOTALLY A RULER.
[AKATSUKI]
IT'S A RULER.
[RODERICK] THE METRO BLADE...
ANY UNIT CAN BE MEASURE
WITH PRECISION,
AND IT'S AUTHENTICITY IS
COMPLETELY CONFIRMED
BY THIS DEVICE!
FIRST WE SHUT DOWN HIS
ABILITY, AND THEN...
[MICHITAKA]
TIGER ECHO FIST! UWAH!
UAAHHHHH!
[MICHITAKA] ANYWAY.
THAT'S THE GIST OF IT.
[SHIROE] THERE WAS ONE MORE...
OKAY, SEINE. GO AHEAD.
[SEINE] UUH...
[SEINE] UH, HELLO EVERYBODY...
[AKATSUKI] MM.
MY NAME IS SEINE... AND...
AND THERE WAS MORE THAN JUST THE
SCANDAL GENIUS
WE REPORTED THE OTHER DAY.
WE ALSO HAD THE SO‐CALLED
"PESTILENCE INCIDENT"
RIGHT BEFORE THE LIBRA FESTIVAL.
AND SISLAU, THE MONSTER WHO
CAUSED IT,
LOVED CALLING HIMSELF
THE POISON GENIUS.
[RODERICK]
OUR BEST GUESS SO FAR IS
THAT A NEW TYPE OF
MONSTER WAS INTRODUCED
WITH THE NOVASPHERE
PIONEERS UPGRADE.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD?
[SHIROE] HMM?
[AKATSUKI]
YOU'RE NOT TIRED, ARE YOU?
[SHIROE]
NO. I'M OKAY.
I'M FEELING JUST FINE.
MPH. ALL RIGHT...
[MINORI]
MASTER SHIROE!
[SHIROE]
HUH?
[MINORI]
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
[SHIROE]
MINORI. IS YOUR SHIFT OVER?
[MINORI] YEAH! THEY GAVE ME LOTS
OF FREE EXTRA STUFF TODAY!
YOU MEAN "EVERY DAY."
YOU NEED HELP?
NAH, I'VE GOT IT.
[MINORI]
AND HERE'S WHY....
TA‐DA! LIFE'S BETTER
WITH A MAGIC BAG!
WOW!
MINORI, YOU DESIGNED THAT?!
(GIGGLEE) I SURE DID!
LOOK! YOU CAN JUST KEEP
ON CRAMMING STUFF IN!
IT'S VERY EFFICIENT! AND
SUPER CHIC AND GIRLY!
[SHIROE]
AHHH...
[SHIROE] WELL, I THINK
WE SHOULD GET SOME
TREATS TO TAKE BACK HOME.
[AKATSUKI] ABSOLUTELY!
RED BEAN BUNS, MY LORD!
[MINORI] COULDN'T WE
EAT SOMETHING LIKE
A FLAN FOR A CHANGE?
[AKATSUKI] YOU GOT A PROBLEM
WITH RED BEAN BUNS?
[MINORI] NO, BUT CHANGE IS GOOD.
[AKATSUKI] HA. IT'S NOT THE
USUAL RED BEAN BUNS TODAY.
THEY'RE CHERRY BLOSSOM BUNS,
A LIMITED SEASONAL EDITION.
[TETORA] OH YEAH? WELL,
[ALL] HUH?
I WANNA HAVE SOME STRAWBERRY
SHORTCAKE! RIGHT NOW!
[SHIROE]
WHA‐?! TETORA?!
GET OFF OF MY LORD.
YOU'RE A NUISANCE, HALF‐STARLET.
[TETORA]
HALF‐STARLET, YOU SAY?!
THE GALAXY TREMBLES
AT MY STARDOM
WHILE THE PLANETS
REVOLVE AROUND ME!
AND SHIROE ALREADY SAID HE
ABSOLUTELY POSITIVELY LOVES IT
[TETORA] WHEN I STICK TO HIS
BODY LIKE THIS ALL DAY LONG!
(LAUGHS)
[SHIROE] NO, I DIDN'T.
[MINORI] SHIROE...
[AKATSUKI] I'LL CUT HER.
STRAWBERRY, STRAWBERRY
SHORTCAKE!
[MINORI] WE ARE GOING TO GET
FLAN! (SHIROE IN PAIN)
THE RED BEAN BUNS ARE THIS WAY,
MY LORD! [SHIROE] YAARGH!
[SHIROE] ARRGGGHHH!
(HORRIFIED)
[KNIGHT A] DEEP FRIED
ROCKFISH FOR ME!
[KNIGHT B]
ME TOO!
[WAITRESS A]
OKAY!
[KARASHIN]
HELLO, ISAAC.
(MUNCH)
[KARASHIN]
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
(GRUNT)
[ISAAC] YOU'VE BEEN
EXTRA CHUMMY LATELY.
[KARASHIN] OH, COME ON...
I'M JUST MEETING A FRIEND
TO DISCUSS BUSINESS OVER DINNER.
CAN I GET A DEEP FRIED
ROCKFISH AND A BEER?
[WAITRESS B] SURE!
(MOUTHFUL) TRYIN' TO
MAKE MONEY HERE?
Y'DON'T HAVE TO PUT
IT THAT WAY...
I'M JUST CHECKIN' IN ON ONE OF
MY GUILD'S FINE ESTABLISHMENTS.
[REZARICK] I DEFINITELY
TOLD YOU BEFORE
THAT THIS IS A TRADING BRANCH
OF SHOPPING DISTRICT
EIGHT, MISTER ISAAC.
[ISAAC] REZARICK. STOP CALLING
ME MISTER. I'M SERIOUS.
[REZARICK] YESSIR.
[KARASHIN] HERE YOU GO.
STRAIGHT FROM THE
ROUND TABLE TO YOU.
[ISAAC] AH.
[KARASHIN] APPARENTLY IT'S A
REPORT ON ENEMIES
THEY CALL "GENIUSES."
THE NAME RINGS A BELL,
BUT WHAT'RE THEY ALL ABOUT?
COULDN'T SAY.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
SOME PEOPLE OF THE LAND
ARE LOOKING TO GO TO WAR.
SHADY BUSINESS ALL
OVER THE PLACE, HUH?
[REZARICK] THEY'RE ALSO SAYING
THE WYVERN DISTURBANCE IN SAPHIR
WAS A SIDE EFFECT OF MINAMI
POWER‐LEVELING PEOPLE
OF THE LAND.
I GET IT NOW... WE'RE IN MAIHAMA
BECAUSE THE VILLAIN KNEW
ALL OF THIS WAS GOING ON...
YEAH, THAT'S SHIROE.
ALWAYS A STEP AHEAD.
[ISAAC] TELL ME ABOUT IT.
[SHIROE] WOW... I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S BEEN ALMOST A YEAR
SINCE WE WERE TRANSPORTED HERE.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
[SHIROE] IT MAKES SENSE
THAT PEOPLE WOULD WANT TO LEAVE.
[NYANTA] YEAH. AND SOME
A LOT MORE THAN OTHERS.
Y'KNOW WHAT I'M SAYIN'?
I UNDERSTAND WHY THEY WOULD.
NONE OF THIS HAS BEEN EASY.
[MARIELLE] OH? YOU'RE HELPING
OUT? [SERARA] YES, MA'AM
[MARIELLE] AHH... I'M GLAD
YOU'RE GETTING THE HANG OF IT.
AND I REMEMBER YOU SAID
YOU'RE ABLE TO MAKE
SIMPLE THINGS ALREADY...
AND YOU DON'T EVEN NEED THE
CHEF SUBCLASS TO DO IT ANYMORE.
WELL THERE'S A LOT
MORE TO IT THAN THAT.
HUH?
[SERARA] ALL DONE!
[NYANTA] NOW THAT'S A
LOVELY DISH, SERARA!
[SERARA] THANKS!
[NYANTA]
WHAT ABOUT THE NEW POTATOES?
[SERARA] I'VE GOT 'EM BOILED UP
AND SPICED JUST
THE WAY YOU LIKE IT!
[NYANTA] YOU KEEP
GETTING BETTER AND BETTER.
WELL, I'VE HAD A
WONDERFUL TEACHER!
WHY DON'T WE HAVE SOME TEA
WHILE WE WAIT FOR THE
VEGETABLES TO COOL DOWN?
SOUNDS GREAT.
(SLIME MOOING)
[NYANTA] IS IT A
GOOD POT THIS TIME?
[SERARA] YES, IT'S
REALLY WARM AND TASTY.
[NYANTA] MY GOODNESS,
WHAT A RELAXING DAY.
I JUST WANNA CURL UP IN
A SUNBEAM AND TAKE A NAP
(BLOW AND SIP)
HMMM.
WELL LOOK AT YOU, YOU SEEM
TO BE ENJOYING YOURSELF.
WELL THAT'S BECAUSE I AM!
[NYANTA] HMM? I'M
GLAD TO HEAR IT.
UH...
UM, IS EVERYTHING OKAY
WITH YOU, CHIEF?
I'M DOING WONDERFUL.
I'M GLAD TO HEAR IT.
[NYANTA]
HEY SERARA,
ARE YOU GLAD YOU ENDED UP HERE
IN THE ELDER TALES WORLD?
[SERARA] HUH? OH! I AM.
ARE YOU SURE YOU MEAN THAT?
YEAH! I MEAN I KNOW I CAN'T SEE
MY MOM OR MY DAD RIGHT NOW,
AND A LOT OF REALLY
STRANGE THINGS
HAVE HAPPENED TO ME
SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE...
BUT A LOT OF GOOD THINGS HAVE
HAPPENED TO ME TOO,
KINDA LIKE...
HMM?
WELL NOW THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANNA BE IN THE FUTURE.
SO YOU HAVE A DREAM THEN?
MM‐HM...
(CHUCKLING)
[NYANTA, THINKING] LOOK AT THAT.
NOT EVERYONE CAME HERE THE
SAME AGE OR THE SAME LEVEL.
BUT WE ALL HAVE ROOM TO GROW.
JUST LIKE CHILDREN EVENTUALLY
BECOME YOUNG ADULTS,
AND THEN THEY GROW SOME
MORE, AND ARE REBORN AGAIN.
AND EVENTUALLY
REINVENT THEMSELVES
INTO WHATEVER THEY WANT.
Y'KNOW I THINK YOU'LL BE FINE.
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING YOU SET
YOUR MIND TO, LITTLE LADY.
[SERARA] OHH... EHH! UHH...
B‐B‐B‐B‐B‐BUT... MY DREAM
IS JUST SO FAR AWAY!
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE I'M
GIVING UP OR ANYTHING!
BUT I KNOW I'VE GOT WORK TO DO.
YOU SEE...? WHEN I COMPARE WHAT
I'VE DONE WITH WHAT
MINORI AND ISUZU HAVE
MANAGED TO DO...
I REALLY HAVEN'T DONE
THAT MUCH AT ALL.
SO I JUST GOTTA WORK TO BE
THE BEST THAT I CAN BE.
AND IT'S GONNA TAKE SOME TIME.
BUT THERE'S ONE THING
I HAVE TO DO FIRST.
I MUST FIND IT WITHIN MYSELF
TO BE STRONG AND INDEPENDENT.
THEN I CAN GET TO WHERE I WANT.
YOU'RE GROWIN' UP.
YAH!
I KNOW THAT
YOU CAN DO IT...
TAKE ALL THE TIME YOU
NEED, UNDERSTAND.
SO YOU KNOW, I'M PULLING FOR YOU
TO GET EVERYTHING YOU WANT
OUT OF LIFE. THAT GOES FOR YOU
AND ALL YOU'RE FRIENDS, TOO.
(HAPPY SIGH)
[SHIROE, THINKING] KANAMI.
I SURE COULD USE YOUR HELP.
I GUESS I SHOULDN'T COMPLAIN.
I WAS BETTER OFF
THAN MOST PEOPLE.
I RAN INTO SOME FRIENDS
RIGHT AWAY WHEN I GOT HERE.
I'M PRETTY LUCKY TO HAVE BOTH
NAOTSUGU AND AKATSUKI AROUND.
FEEL FREE TO THANK ME IN
PERSON. I'M RIGHT HERE.
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
I DID SOME
NINJA STUFF.
YOU'RE REALLY GETTING
THIS NINJA THING DOWN.
I'M GLAD YOU NOTICED, MY LORD.
AH...
SO TELL ME...
WHAT SEEMS TO BE TROUBLING
YOU NOW? [SHIROE] HUH?
[SHIROE] EH?
[AKATSUKI] I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
WHEN SOMETHING IS BOTHER YOU,
YOUR FOREHEAD GETS ALL
WRINKLY LIKE AN OLD MAN.
OH, IT DOES?
I WOULDN'T LIE TO YOU.
HEY! SHIROE, I FINALLY
FOUND YOU! UWAHH!
[TETORA] MY NAUGHTY RADAR
IS GOING OFF!
IS THIS A MIDNIGHT TRYST?
[NAOTSUGU] ERK!
[TETORA] YOU'RE GOING
OVER BORING STRATEGY
STUFF AGAIN, AREN'T CHA?!
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, ARE YOU
GUYS DISCUSSING STRATEGY?
HEY! COME HERE!
[TETORA] OOPSY DAISY!
AN ADORABLE FACE,
ATTRACTIVE BEYOND A DOUBT...
WELL I'M RIGHT HERE!
YOU'RE GONNA NEED A GALACTIC
SUPERSTAR IN ON THIS PUPPY!
NOT TO MENTION
YOUR FAVORITE TANK!
[SHIROE] YOU TWO HAVE
BECOME QUITE A PAIR.
[NAOTSUGU] TH‐TH‐TH‐THAT'S
NOT EVEN FUNNY!
[TETORA] YOU KNOW WE'RE
MEANT FOR EACH OTHER!
JUST CALL US,
"TETOTSUGU" FROM NOW ON.
THE GUARDIAN'S TOTALLY
MASSIVE AND TOWERING ARMOR
GETS PROTECTED BY MY
REACTIVE HEALING SPELL!
EVERY TIME HE GETS BEAT UP,
THE POWER OF MY STARDOM...
AS WELL AS MY LOVE WILL MAKE
HIS HEART POUND FOR ME.
[NAOTSUGU] UGH... JUST... DON'T.
OH, NAOTSUGU,
YOU'RE SUCH A TEASE.
(TETORA GIGGLING)
UH‐HUH...
[TETORA] SO WHAT NOW?
[SHIROE] IT'S BEEN ALMOST A YEAR
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE
BROUGHT US HERE.
THERE ARE A LOT OF ADVENTURERS
WHO HAVEN'T BEEN TO ADJUST,
AND THEY JUST WANNA GO HOME.
[AKATSUKI] BUT THAT'S NOT
REALLY AN OPTION FOR US, IS IT?
[SHIROE] DON'T THINK SO...
AND WELL, EINS SAYS
WE SHOULD FIND A WAY
TO HELP THOSE PEOPLE.
[NAOTSUGU] YOU MEAN WHAT
HE SAID ABOUT LEVYING A TAX
ON THE WEALTHY AND
STARTING A WELFARE STATE?
[TETORA] YOU THINK SOMETHING
LIKE THAT'S REALLY GONNA WORK.
[SHIROE] I'M GUESSING IT WON'T.
[AKATSUKI] NO, OF COURSE NOT.
FOR NOW, I THINK THEY'RE ONLY
ONE WAY WE CAN POSSIBLY
HELP THEM. AND THAT'S TO TRY AND
GET THEM BACK TO THE OLD WORLD.
AND DO IT SOON...
THE ENTIRE SERVER'S
ABOUT TO GO TO WAR.
[TETORA] YOU MIGHT
BE RIGHT. (BLOW)
YES. AND IT COULD BE POSSIBLE
THAT OUR VERY EXISTENCE HERE
IN THE WORLD IS
ULTIMATELY THE CAUSE.
SO WHAT YOU'RE TELLING US...
IS THAT WE MIGHT
ACTUALLY HAVE A DUTY
TO FIND OUR WAY
BACK HOME, MY LORD?
HMPH...
[SHIROE] THERE'S SOMETHING
EXTREMELY IMPORTANT
THAT I NEED TO TELL ALL OF YOU.
[ALL] HMM?
[NYANTA] OH YEAH?
WELL LET'S HEAR WHAT IT
IS YOU HAVE TO SAY, MY MAN
HEY CHIEF.
HMM?
[AKATSUKI] A LETTER?
[NAOTSUGU] A LOOOOVE LETTER?
[SHIROE] YEAH, NO THAT
WOULD HAVE BEEN NICE.
HMM?!
THE LETTER'S
FROM ROE2.
SHE'S MY SECOND
CHARACTER.
[TETORA] OOOH...
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE AVATAR
YOU LEFT ON THE TEST
SERVER, RIGHT?
YOU GOT HER TO LEVEL 90?
COME ON! ARE WE
REALLY TALKING ABOUT
THE TEST SERVER? THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE ON THE MOON!
[SHIROE] MM‐HM.
[AKATSUKI] THE MOON...?
AND YOUR BETA CHARACTER'S
WRITING YOU LETTERS NOW?
I MEAN, HOW DID THE THING
GET HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE?
[SHIROE] MINORI GAVE
IT TO ME, ACTUALLY.
THE JUNIOR MEMBERS
MET HER ON THE ROAD.
[TETORA] HM...
[SHIROE] ANYWAY...
ACCORDING TO THIS, THE PERSON
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO FIND
SINCE WE GOT HERE...
HAS INSTEAD FOUND ME.
SO IT'S GOT ME THINKING AGAIN.
WHAT IS THE REAL REASON WE WERE
ALL BROUGHT TO THIS WORLD,
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
IT'S STRANGE, DON'T YOU THINK?
IF THIS IS TRULY AN
ALTERNATIVE UNIVERSE,
THEN IT SEEMS UNREASONABLE
THAT IT WOULD BE SO SIMILAR
TO ELDER TALES, RIGHT?
AND BESIDES, THE IDEA
THAT A GAME BECAME REAL
AND SOMEHOW TRANSPORTED
US ALL HERE?
THE THOUGHT OF THAT...
IS IMPOSSIBLE.
AND AS FAR AS WE ALL KNOW,
THERE'S NO TECHNOLOGY THAT
COULD DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
[AKATSUKI] TRUE.
[TETORA] I KNOW, RIGHT?
[SHIROE] AND THE CHANGES
AFTER THE APOCALYPSE
DIDN'T MAKE ANY SENSE EITHER.
THE LAWS OF THE PHYSICAL WORLD
AND THE MECHANICS OF THE GAME
HAVE BEEN JUMBLED TOGETHER.
IT'S AS IF TWO SETS OF RULES
WERE ALMOST RANDOMLY MIXED.
[NAOTUSGU] IT STILL ACTS LIKE
THE GAME IN THE WEIRDEST WAYS.
[SHIROE] IN ANY CASE, I DON'T
THINK THE IDEA OF THIS BEING
AN ALTERNATIVE UNIVERSE
IS PLAUSIBLE ANYMORE...
BUT SOMEONE MUST KNOW... THEY
KNOW WHY WE'RE HERE,
AND THEY KNOW HOW WE WERE
BROUGHT HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
BUT SO FAR, WE HAVEN'T FOUND A
PERSON OF THE LAND OR A PLAYER
LIKE US, WHO CAN EXPLAIN ANY
OF THIS IN FULL DETAIL.
[NAOTSUGU] SO THAT WOULD BE THE
BUTT‐WAD THAT BROUGHT US HERE.
[NYANTA] SO WHAT DOES
THE LETTER SAY?
[SHIROE] ROE2 SAYS SHE TOOK
OVER MY UNUSED SECOND AVATAR...
BASICALLY SHE FOUND HERSELF
A BODY WITHOUT A SOUL,
SO SHE COULD COME TO THIS WORLD.
SO WHO IS SHE ANYWAY?
[SHIROE] SHE REFERS TO HERSELF
HERE AS A "TRAVELLER."
AN INTELLIGENT ENTITY FROM
ANOTHER WORLD. YOU MIGHT CALL
HER AN "ALTERNATE LIFE FORM," OR
EVEN AN "ALIEN" FOR THAT MATTER.
(AKATSUKI INHALES)
[SHIROE] SHE COMES FROM A RACE
OF ARTIFICIALLY CREATED
LIVING BEINGS...
AND SHE SAYS THERE ARE TWO
TYPES,
THERE ARE "OBSERVERS,"
AND OTHERS SHE REFERS
TO AS "COLLECTORS."
THESE TRAVELLERS WERE
CREATED WITH THE MISSION
OF GATHERING A VALUABLE
RESOURCE,
SOMETHING CALLED "EMPATHIUM"
OKAY, AND THAT IS...?
UNFORTUNATELY, THE LETTER DIDN'T
REALLY SAY MUCH MORE, HOWEVER,
SHE DOES SAY THAT HER PEOPLE
EXHAUSTED THEIR EMPATHIUM
AND ENTERED A PERIOD
OF RAPID DECLINE.
[SHIROE/ROE2] "IN ORDER TO
OVERCOME THE SITUATION
WE NEEDED TO HARVEST IT
FROM A DIFFERENT WORLD.
AND LIFE FORMS LIKE ME
WERE CREATED TO SURVEY
THE ALTERNATIVE UNIVERSES
TO RESTOCK THE SUPPLY."
ROE2 AND THE OTHERS GOT HERE
THROUGH SOMETHING CALLED
"THE ECLIPSE." AND OF COURSE
THAT SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
IT'S THEIR VERSION
OF THE APOCALYPSE.
[NAOTSUGU] WAIT, YOU'RE SAYING
THEY KNOW WHAT CAUSED ALL THIS?
[SHIROE] THEY DON'T... IT LOOKS
LIKE THE WHOLE THING'S JUST
AS MUCH A MYSTERY TO THEM TOO.
OKAY. YOU THINK THEY EVER GOT
AHOLD OF
THIS EMPATHIUM
THINGY‐MA‐BOB?
I DON'T KNOW...
[ROE2, VOICEOVER] WE UNDERSTAND
YOUR PEOPLE TO BE INTELLIGENT
ENTITIES THAT ARE
RANK 3 OR HIGHER.
MINORI AND HER FRIENDS HAVE
PROVEN THEMSELVES TO BE SUCH.
CONSEQUENTLY, YOUR PEOPLE
RESERVE
THE RIGHTS TO THE
RESOURCES IN THIS WORLD.
COLLECTORS HAVE BEEN ORDERED
TO PRIORITIZE ACQUISITION,
BUT OUR MISSION AS OBSERVERS
IS TO CONTINUE INVESTIGATION.
[SHIROE/ROE2] "I HAVE NO IDEA IF
MY OLDER BROTHER,
SHIROE IS GONNA END UP
READING THIS LETTER,
BUT IF YOU DO, YOU ARE GOING
TO NEED A TRANSMITTER
TO COMMUNICATE WITH THE MOON."
[AKATSUKI] AH...
[ROE2] AS YOU MAY KNOW...
WE HAVE A COMMUNITY ON THE MOON
WATCHING OVER THE SITUATION.
[ROE2, VOICEOVER] AND IF ANY OF
YOUR PEOPLE WISH TO "RETURN,"
THERE IS A POSSIBILITY
WE CAN ASSIST YOU.
(GASP)
[ROE2, VOICEOVER]
BUT AS A WORD OF WARNING,
BEWARE THE COLLECTORS.
THEY ARE TRAVELLERS LIKE US,
BUT THEIR INTELLIGENCE
IS ONLY AROUND RANK 2.
THEY CAME TO THIS WORLD USING
PRE‐EXISTING MONSTER
CHARACTERS WITH
HIGH COMBAT SKILLS.
AND AS YOU'LL SEE, IF
YOU HAVEN'T ALREADY,
THEY'RE NOT EASY
TO GET ALONG WITH.
[SHIROE] "AND SO I MUST ADVISE
YOU TO BE EXTREMELY CAUTIOUS.
[ALL] HMMM...
[SHIROE] SO WE CAN
ASSUME, I GUESS,
THAT THE "GENIUSES" ARE
THESE "COLLECTORS"
SHE'S TALKING ABOUT.
WHY IN THE HELL WOULD THEY
BE TARGETING
ADVENTURERS THEN, HUH?
[NYANTA] HMMM...
[SHIROE] I'M NOT SURE.
[ROE2] P. S. DEAREST MINORI,
IT WAS A PLEASURE
MEETING YOU AND ALL THE OTHERS.
MAY THE WARM GLOW
OF YOUR EMPATHIUM,
LIGHT THE WAY TO WHEREVER
YOUR FUTURE TAKES YOU.
LOVE, YOUR BIG SIS.
[SHIROE] THERE'S STILL A LOT
ABOUT THIS I DON'T UNDERSTAND...
BUT IF WE CAN FIND
A WAY TO GET IN TOUCH
WITH THE OBSERVERS SHE
SAYS ARE UP ON THE MOON,
THEY MIGHT ACTUALLY BE ABLE TO
GIVE US A HINT
ABOUT HOW TO GET BACK HOME.
[TETORA] SO YOU'RE REALLY GONNA
TRUST WHAT'S IN THAT LETTER?
[SHIROE]
I THINK WE CAN, TETORA.
[NYANTA] IS THERE ANY PARTICULAR
REASON WHY YOU TRUST IT.
WHEN I DIED IN THE ABYSSAL
SHAFT, I SAW SOMETHING.
IT WAS A BEACH...
ON THE MOON...
AND NOW THAT I'VE
READ THIS LETTER,
I'M PRETTY SURE...
IT WASN'T, IT WASN'T A DREAM.
I SAW IT... I WAS WITH YOU.
I REMEMBER ALL THE MEMORIES
FLOATING INTO THE SKY.
THAT REALLY HAPPENED, IT DID.
MPH...
[TETORA] HMM...
HM?
(TETORA GIGGLES)
[SHIROE] SO IF WE CAN GET THERE,
JUST ONE MORE TIME...
WE MIGHT...
WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO GET BACK HOME!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] MEET
RAYNESHIA'S YOUNGER BROTHER,
AND MAIHAMA'S PRINCE, ITHERUS.
A BIRTHDAY PARTY IS
HELD IN HIS HONOR
TO ANNOUNCE HIS
SUCCESSION TO LORD.
BUT EVEN DURING
SUCH FESTIVITIES,
THE THREAT OF WAR
HANGS OVER THE LAND.
AN INSIDIOUS SHADOW THREATENS
THE YOUNG BOY'S LIFE,
AND PROVOKES AN ENRAGED
BLACK SWORD KNIGHT.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.