(CHRISTMAS MUSIC)
[SOJIRO] CHRISTMAS IS PRETTY
NICE DON'T YOU THINK, LADIES?
I SERIOUSLY CAN'T WAIT!
WHY DON'T WE GET
THE GUILD TOGETHER
FOR A CHRISTMAS EVE PARTY?
[CHIKA] YEAH THAT SOUNDS GREAT!
YOU CAN COUNT ME IN!
I'M ALL FOR A CELEBRATION,
AS LONG AS WE GET CHICKEN
AND CAKE ALL NIGHT LONG!
SO, IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
YOU THINK WE NEED TO HAVE?
WELL, YOU KNOW, SINCE
IT'S CHRISTMAS AND ALL...
MAYBE WE COULD
TRY SOME SALMON.
[ALL] SALMON?
MMM, WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO
HAVE SALMON ON CHRISTMAS?
I THINK IT'LL BE PERFECT!
LET'S DO IT!
YEAH! YOU GUYS ARE
GONNA LOVE IT!
(LAUGHS)
[RAYNESHIA]
NOW WAIT A MINUTE.
DON'T YOU THINK THIS IS
A LITTLE TOO SHORT?
I REALLY DON'T WANNA SHOW OFF
MY LEGS TOO MUCH.
OH, IT'S ADORABLE
ON YOU, NESSIE!
YOU LOOK
ABSOLUTELY STUNNING!
[HENRIETTA]
JUST A SKOSH ABOVE THE KNEES
IS A PERFECT FIT FOR YOU!
[SERARA] YOU LOOK
REALLY PRETTY, PRINCESS!
I MUST ADMIT I'M NOT VERY
KNOWLEDGEABLE
OF ALL YOUR CHRISTMAS CUSTOMS...
BUT ISN'T THIS "SANTA CLAUS"
YOU WANNA SEE
SUPPOSED TO BE LIKE AN
OLDER, HEAVIER GENTLEMAN?
MM‐HM. THAT'S CORRECT.
[MARIELLE]
AH AKATSUKI, WHAT'VE YOU DONE?!
I AM SO GONNA HAVE TO PUNISH YOU
FOR THAT LITTLE INDISCRETION!
[AKATSUKI] EHH?
(ANNOYED)
WOW! BOTH OF YOU ARE SUPER CUTE!
YOU'RE AS TASTY AS
A HUNDRED CHICKENS!
MAKE SURE YOU HAVE ROOM
FOR SOME SUPPER, YOU GUYS!
(ANNOYED NOISE)
[RIEZE] YES, OF COURSE
[AKATSUKI] HUH?
[ALL] HUH?
[RIEZE] THEY APPEAR TO BE
DRESSED AS REINDEER
AND A SANTA CLAUS
IN A MINISKIRT.
THEY LOOK VERY CUTE.
[RAYNESHIA] LADY RIEZE,
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
I AM REPORTING TO
MASTER KRUSTY.
(BOTH GASP)
I'M JUST KIDDING,
IT WAS JUST A FRIEND.
(SIGH OF RELIEF)
[RAYNESHIA]
THANK GOODNESS!
WHO KNOWS WHAT THAT
MONSTER WOULD DO
IF HE KNEW ALL
THIS WAS GOING ON!
[RIEZE] I APOLOGIZE.
THAT WAS A TAD DESPICABLE.
IT'S JUST YOU TWO ARE SO
TAKEN WITH EACH OTHER,
I COULDN'T HELP MYSELF...
[RAYNESHIA]
HUH?
(DOOR OPENING)
[MIKAKAGE] PARDON ME, LADIES!
(SMALL LAUGH)
[MIKAKAGE]
WE BROUGHT YOU SOME SNACKIES.
[ALL]
YOU'RE AWESOME! THANK YOU!
HMMMM...
MMMM...
MMMMMM...
(QUIET GIGGLE)
[ALI] OH...
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
STRANGE.
WHEN I FIRST GOT HERE,
AKATSUKI WAS MY ONLY GUARD.
[RAYNESHIA]
WOW, THIS IS GOOD!
THIS FRUITCAKE IS REALLY
DELICIOUS! THANK YOU!
[MIKAKAGE]
UH‐HUH!
[MARIELLE] MIKAKAGE IS
A MASTER OF EVERYTHING
FROM APPETIZERS TO DESSERTS!
BAKING AND PREPARATION OF
SWEETS IS AN ART FORM FOR ME,
EVERYTHING ELSE IN THE
KITCHEN IS JUST A HOBBY!
YOUR COOKING IS RIGHT
UP THERE WITH MR. CAT'S.
I LIKE GUARDING A PRINCESS;
AND THE FRINGE BENEFITS AND
PERKS AREN'T BAD EITHER,
NOT TO MENTION TASTY.
SO ABOUT THE PEOPLE
IN D. D. D.,
WHEN ARE YOU
EXPECTING THEM BACK?
EVEN THOUGH THEY'VE
DONE A GREAT DEAL
TO VANQUISH THE LATEST
GOBLIN ASSAULT,
IT WON'T BE UNTIL NEW YEARS.
AND HERE I WAS HOPING TO HAVE
THEM BACK BY CHRISTMAS.
POOPY‐TOOTS, WE WERE GONNA
THROW THEM A PARTY.
IT'S LIKE EVERYONE'S
SO BUSY THESE DAYS,
I HAVEN'T SEEN
MASTER SHIROE IN FOREVER.
DID HE LOCK HIMSELF
IN HIS ROOM AGAIN?
UH, YOU SEE‐
[HENRIETTA] WELL, IF HE'S
BEING HIS USUAL SELF,
THEN SHIROE ISN'T GOING TO
POP HIS HEAD UP
FOR CHRISTMAS ANYWAY.
AND HE PROBABLY HAS
A LOT OF WORK
TO FINISH BEFORE THE NEW YEAR.
YEAH, I SUPPOSE...
I GUESS IT'S SAFE TO SAY
ALL OF YOU ARE KEEPING BUSY.
(EXHALE)
[MARIELLE] SO LONG, PRINCESS!
SEE YA AROUND.
[RIEZE]
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
[AKATSUKI]
BYE.
[RAYNESHIA]
AH, MISS AKATSUKI!
OH...?
I, UH... I APPRECIATE
WHAT YOU DID TODAY.
HUH?
THANKS FOR DRESSING UP IN
THOSE BIZARRE OUTFITS WITH ME.
YEAH, WELL... THEY KINDA
FORCED ME TO WEAR THAT.
SURE, BUT I KNOW YOU'VE BEEN
DROPPING BY TO SEE ME EVERY DAY.
AND IT'S JUST REALLY NICE OF
YOU TO COME BY AND CHECK ON ME.
[RAYNESHIA]
THANK YOU.
AH...!
WELL I WAS... JUST DOING MY JOB.
SEE YOU TOMORROW
YEAH!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
WHEN DID I ALLOW MYSELF
TO BECOME SO WEAK?
IT'S MY JOB TO
GUARD THE PRINCESS.
I SHOULD BE PLEASED THAT MY LORD
ENTRUSTED ME WITH SUCH A TASK...
BUT IT HURTS TO THINK THAT
HE'S REALLY WORRIED ABOUT HER.
WHAT IF I WAS MORE LIKE HER...?
I MEAN WOULD IT CHANGE THE WAY
HE THINKS ABOUT ME?
WOULD HE WORRY ABOUT ME?
ON THE OTHER HAND, IF I WAS
LIKE THE PRINCESS...
I NEVER WOULD HAVE STOOD BY
MY LORD'S SIDE AS AN ASSASSIN.
I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO PROTECT
HIM IF I'M NOTHING BUT SMILES
AND CHARM AND DESSERTS
ALL THE TIME.
(GASP)
UH, HEY...! I'M SORRY AND
I DON'T WANNA BOTHER YOU AGAIN,
BUT WHAT HAPPENED TO THE
SWORD THAT WAS ON DISPLAY?
I SOLD IT.
OH? NO, YOU DID?
[TATARA] YES. AND THE MAN EVEN
PAID FOR IT STRAIGHT UP IN GOLD.
UH...
(SHAKY INHALE)
[RIEZE] HAS AKATSUKI SEEMED
TROUBLED TO YOU LATELY?
[HENRIETTA]
I GUESS IT WASN'T JUST ME, HUH?
NO... SHE DOESN'T SEEM LIKE THE
KIND OF PERSON
WHO LETS IT SHOW, EITHER.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE...
WELL, SOMETHING IS GOING ON.
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S
BEEN WATCHING
D. D. D.'S TRAINING
SESSIONS LATELY.
HUH?
[RIEZE]
I'VE ONLY SEEN HER ONCE,
BUT I THINK SHE'S
BEEN THERE BEFORE.
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S
UNWELCOME, YOU KNOW?
ALL SHE HAS TO DO IS ASK,
AND SHE CAN PARTICIPATE IN
A RAID WITH US IN D. D. D.
WE ARE THE BEST IN AKIHABARA.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN
SIMPLY FORCE HER TO JOIN US.
AND WHEN I LET LORD KRUSTY KNOW,
HE JUST SAID TO LET AKATSUKI
LOOK ON AS MUCH AS SHE WISHES.
HE SAID THAT HE OWES
SHIROE A FAVOR.
AND THAT IS SOMETHING HAPPENS,
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GIVE HER
WHATEVER HELP WE CAN.
WELL THAT'S CERTAINLY
NEWS TO ME...
BUT IF THAT'S THE CASE,
SHE MIGHT BE SPENDING TIME
SPYING ON THE
OTHER GUILDS AS WELL.
I GUESS SHE'S CONCERNED
ABOUT HER ABILITIES,
AND IF SHE HAS WHAT IT
TAKES TO GET THE JOB DONE.
[HENRIETTA] I KINDA GET
THE FEELING SHE'S GOT
SOMETHING ELSE ON HER MIND.
[RIEZE] OHH...?
IT'S MORE LIKE WHAT SHE'S
LACKING IS... CONFIDENCE.
[RIEZE]
HM....
[HENRIETTA]
I SUPPOSE, FOR RIGHT NOW,
ALL WE CAN DO IS
BE THERE FOR HER.
[RIEZE]
FAIR ENOUGH.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
THE ORAL ARTS...
WELL BROTHER SHIROE
SAID THEY EXIST.
HUH... HE REALLY DID?
[TOYA] YEAH, HE SAID THAT
THEY'RE TOTALLY LEGIT.
(COMBAT NOISES)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
IF MY LORD SAID THEY EXIST,
THEN THERE'S NO DOUBT
THE ORAL ARTS ARE REAL!
LARGE RAID GUILDS LIKE D. D. D.
AND BLACK SWORD KNIGHTS
SHOULD HAVE
FIRST‐RATE ASSASSINS.
IF THEIR ASSASSINS ARE
USING THE ORAL ARTS,
I WANT TO SEE JUST HOW
STRONG THEY TRULY ARE.
I'LL WATCH UNTIL I ACTUALLY SEE
ONE OF THEM USE ONE.
THEY HAVE TO BE EVENLY MATCHED
AND WILLING TO BREAK A DEADLOCK.
[GUY C]
YOU GOTTA STEP INTO IT!
[GUY D] THAT WAS JUST SAD!
PICK UP THE PACE, YOU GUYS!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
IF I KNEW EVEN ONE ORAL ART,
HOW POWERFUL COULD I BECOME?
(HUMMING A TUNE)
OH! HEY, AKATSUKI!
WELCOME BACK!
WE'RE GONNA HAVE BOUILLABAISSE
TODAY, YOU GUYS.
PULL UP A SEAT...
WE'RE ALMOST READY TO GET
DIN‐DIN STARTED, NYAH.
I THINK I'LL... PASS.
[MINORI] HUH?
[ISUZU] OH COME ON!
IT TURNED OUT REALLY GOOD!
AND RUDY AND TOYA ARE GONNA
BE BACK ANY MINUTE NOW.
[AKATSUKI] NN‐NM... SORRY,
BUT I'M JUST NOT HUNGRY.
UH... WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO HER?
SHE HASN'T BEEN ACTING
LIKE HERSELF FOR A WHILE.
UH YEAH... HMM...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] PERFECT
LITTLE MIDDLE SCHOOL PRISS!
THAT SMUG LITTLE, STUPID
IMMATURE, KNOW‐IT‐ALL.
WHO THE HELL DOES SHE
THINK SHE IS, ANYWAY?
I SHOULD BE ASHAMED OF MYSELF!
WHENEVER I SEE HER, I CAN'T HELP
BUT GET JEALOUS AND ANGRY.
IT MAKES ME FEEL UGLY INSIDE...
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S
SLACKING OFF. SHE ISN'T!
SHE'S TRYING REALLY HARD!
I'LL WORK AT LEAST
AS HARD AS YOU...
I'LL DO ALL I CAN.
MINORI, I DON'T WANT TO CAUSE
YOU ANY PROBLEMS.
I'LL DO MY BEST TO AVOID THEM.
UH, UM, THANK YOU...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] MINORI WAS
HELPING MY LORD GET THINGS DONE,
WHILE I WAS WASTING TIME
THINKING ABOUT MYSELF.
I DIDN'T GIVE HIM
ANY HELP AT ALL...
I WAS THERE THE WHOLE TIME
BUT I DIDN'T ASSIST HIM WITH
ANYTHING. I WAS SO USELESS.
I'VE NEVER BEEN IN
A RAID OR A QUEST,
WHICH MAKE ME A
SECOND‐RATE ASSASSIN.
I CAN'T EVEN BUY A WEAPON
THAT'LL HELP ME IN A RAID.
THAT'S WHY HE DIDN'T
TAKE ME WITH HIM.
ALL I CAN DO IS FIGHT,
BUT I'M WEAK.
SO, THERE'S REALLY ONLY
ONE THING I CAN WORK TOWARD.
I NEED STRENGTH,
BUT HOW DO I GET IT?
WE'VE CERTAINLY BECOME QUITE
THE HUB OF ACTIVITY LATELY?
WILL THEY BE COMING
BACK AGAIN TOMORROW?
YES, THEY'RE SHOWING ME
AROUND THE CITY.
OH, IS THAT RIGHT? WELL YOU
SHOULD AT LEAST FEEL SAFE,
WITH A WHOLE TROOP OF MIGHTY
ADVENTURERS GUARDING YOU.
THEY TOLD ME THAT WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE A DISH CALLED
A "CREAM STEW"
FOR DINNER TONIGHT.
[ELISSA] INTERESTING... I GUESS
IT'LL BE "ADVENTURER STYLE"?
YEAH, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
(YAWN)
[RAYNESHIA] IT SEEMS LIKE
A LOT OF THINGS HAVE BEEN
"ADVENTURER STYLE" LATELY...
THEY WANTED ME TO DRESS UP
LIKE SOMEONE CALLED,
"SANTA CLAUS" TODAY.
[ELISSA] AH YES, I ASKED THEM
TO BRING SOME OF THEIR CLOTHES,
AND I GUESS THAT'S WHAT THEY
DECIDED TO PICK FOR YOU.
HUH?
THE IDEA WAS TO GET YOU FAMILIAR
WITH THEIR STYLE OF CLOTHING.
PERHAPS THAT WAS JUST
THEIR WAY OF INCLUDING YOU.
(SIGH)
KAY, WELL THAT EXPLAINS IT.
YOU KNOW? TRYING ON
ALL OF THOSE CLOTHES
KINDA MADE ME A LITTLE SLEEPY.
REALLY? WELL IT MIGHT NOT BE
MY PLACE TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT IT LOOKED LIKE YOU WERE
ENJOYING YOURSELF.
[RAYNESHIA] UH?
[ELISSA]
IT DOES MY HEART GOOD
TO SEE YOU MAKING
SOME FRIENDS, MILADY.
LOOK, THOSE PEOPLE
ARE NOT MY FRIENDS.
HUH? BUT YOU WERE HAVING
SUCH A NICE TIME.
AND IT APPEARED TO ME LIKE
THEY'D BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO HELP IF YOU EVER
GET INTO TROUBLE.
TALKING WITH THEM IS NOT WHAT
I WOULD CALL A NICE TIME.
I HAVE TO BE WARY.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY'RE
NORMAL LIKE WE ARE, OKAY.
THEY'LL ALWAYS BE ADVENTURERS.
YES, BUT MILADY...
[RAYNESHIA] I'VE MASTERED
MANY FORMS OF ETIQUETTE,
BUT THEY ARE DIFFERENT.
IF YOU'RE HAPPY, ACT HAPPY.
IF YOU'RE SAD, ACT SAD.
EMOTIONS ARE WHAT THEY ARE...
AND THEY HAVE TO BE EXPRESSED.
IT'S LIKE THEY DON'T KNOW HOW
YOU FEEL UNLESS YOU SHOW THEM...
LET'S FACE IT. I'M USUALLY LAZY,
IRRESPONSIBLE, AND SPINELESS.
THAT'S HOW I'VE ALWAYS BEEN.
AND I'M NOT CHANGING.
I WAS BORN INTO THIS.
I REALLY DO HATE
PLAYING POLITICS.
[ELISSA, THINKING]
I UNDERSTAND, YOUR MAJESTY.
I'M SURE IT'S DIFFICULT
BEING A NOBLEWOMAN,
NEVER HAVING THE LUXURY OF
BEING TRUE TO YOURSELF.
ALTHOUGH, MILADY,
THAT DOESN'T SEEM TO
STOP YOU WHEN HE'S AROUND.
[MISA] ALL MEMBERS
ARE LEVELING UP
AND GAINING ITEMS ON SCHEDULE.
IF WE CAN KEEP THIS UP
INTO THE SPRING,
AKIHABARA'S BATTLE GUILDS
AND SECURITY
WILL BE STRONGER AS A UNIT
WHEN WE RETURN.
MILORD?
HUH? YES.
YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
Y'KNOW NOW'S NOT A GOOD TIME
FOR YOU TO LOSE INTEREST.
DO YOU NEED A NEW TOY
OR SOMETHING
TO KEEP YOU COMPANY, MASTER?
DON'T BE SILLY!
JUST LET ME KNOW WHEN...
THE GOBLINS START MOVING.
(SIGH) WHAT'S HIS DEAL...
[RODERICK]
JUST PUT IT WHERE WE USUALLY DO.
[NYANTA]
GOT A MINUTE, RODERICK?
[RODERICK]
HUH?
[NYANTA] IT'S GOOD TO
SEE YOU THIS FINE EVENING.
[RODERICK]
HMMM?! THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT...
I MEAN IT WAS BARELY NOON
THE LAST TIME I CHECKED.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA
TO SKIP LUNCH, MY MAN.
I NEED TO ASK YOU A
FEW QUESTIONS ANYWAY.
WOULD YOU CARE TO
JOIN ME FOR LUNCH?
IT'S TIME FOR DINNER,
BUT THAT'S FINE BY ME.
OH RIGHT, THEN LET'S
GET SOME RAMEN.
SURE. RAMEN SOUNDS GOOD.
[RAMEN MAN]
THERE YOU GO, GENTLEMEN!
[NYANTA] SO, HOW IS THE
INVENTORY PROJECT
COMING ALONG, MYAH?
[RODERICK] IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'LL NEED SOME OF THE BEST
EPIC‐CLASS ITEMS AND
A FEW SECRET ITEMS AS WELL.
AND YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT
TALKING ABOUT ONE OR TWO.
IT'S KINDA STRANGE,
WHY DO WE NEED TO GO OUT OF
OUR WAY TO ADD FLAVOR TEXT
TO ALL THESE THINGS NOW?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT
MIGHT BE GOING ON HERE?
(BLOWING)
NNHNNN.
[RODERICK] I'LL ADMIT, I CAN SEE
HOW MY MERCHANT GUILD
HAPPENS TO BE THE RIGHT ONE
TO GET THE JOB DONE.
WE CAN RAISE THE MONEY TO GET
THE RESEARCH FINISHED,
AND A SMALLER GUILD ISN'T
IN THE POSITION TO DO THAT.
WE DO APPRECIATE
EVERYTHING YOU'RE DOING.
YOU KNOW WHEN SHIROE ASKS ME
TO TAKE ON A PROJECT LIKE THIS,
IT CERTAINLY MAKES ME WANT TO DO
IT RIGHT.
AND I'M GUESSING THAT
HE WANTS IT DONE QUICKLY
ON TOP OF EVERYTHING ELSE.
(SLURP) MMM‐MM.
WELL FAST IS GOOD, BUT DOING
IT RIGHT IS EVEN BETTER.
(PING) [SHIROE, VOICE CHAT]
HEY CHIEF,
DID I CATCH YOU AT A BAD TIME?
ACTUALLY, YOU CALLED AT
THE PERFECT TIME, MY MAN!
I JUST FINISHED HAVING A LITTLE
CHAT WITH OUR BOY, RODERICK.
[SHIROE] THANKS A LOT, CHIEF.
I SHOULD'VE BEEN BACK BY NOW
TO TAKE CARE OF THAT.
[NYANTA] DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, OLD FRIEND!
I EVEN MANAGED TO GET
SOME DELICIOUS RAMEN OUT OF
THE VISIT. NO WORRIES.
HOW'S EVERYONE BACK HOME DOING?
AH, IT'S GOING PRETTY
WELL AROUND HERE;
THE CITY'S IN HIGH SPIRITS OVER
CHRISTMAS, OF COURSE, MYAH.
[SHIROE]
OH, YEAH, I ALMOST FORGOT.
UH, HOW'S
AKATSUKI DOING?
SHE'S DROPPING IN
ON PRINCESS RAYNESHIA
EVERY DAY TO GUARD HER,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN, MYAH.
[SHIROE]
IS THAT RIGHT?
I'LL LET YOU KNOW IF
ANYTHING CHANGES ON OUR END.
SO WHAT DID HE HAVE TO SAY?
HE SAID IT'S ALL
GOOD BACK THERE.
AND HE ALSO SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
EVERYONE GETTING ALL
REVVED UP FOR CHRISTMAS.
AW MAN, WE'RE NOT MAKIN'
IT BACK IN FIVE DAYS.
MPH.
(BATTLE CRY)
WHAT THE... HUH?
WAHHHH!
'KAY, THAT'S GOOD!
HEHEH
(GROANS OF PAIN)
[HISAKO, CHIKA, SANDY]
THANK YOU FOR SPARRING WITH US!
[HISAKO] THAT WAS INCREDIBLE,
KYOKO! YOU'RE REALLY STRONG.
[KYOKO]
WELL, I AM LEVEL 90, YOU GUYS.
[CHIKA]
PLEASE TELL ME THE SECRET
TO YOUR STRENGTH, MISS KYOKO!
MISS AKATSUKI...
[MARIELLE]
THIS IS JUST LOVELY!
[HENRIETTA]
I DIDN'T THINK I'D EVER FIND
SOMETHING LIKE THIS HERE!
LET'S GET ONE FOR THE MANSION.
IT WILL BRIGHTEN UP ANY ROOM!
[MARIELLE] GOOD IDEA!
I JUST KNOW THAT
NESSIE WILL LOVE IT!
YOU SHOULDN'T CALL HER THAT.
RAYNESHIA'S A PRINCESS,
MARIELLE. UNDERSTAND?
NAH. SHE'S FINE WITH IT,
SHE GAVE ME A SMILE
WHEN I SAID IT! OH LOOK!
[HENRIETTA]
UH... HUH?
[MARIELLE]
AHHHH!
[HENRIETTA]
AH, FOR NAOTSUGU, RIGHT?
HUH? UHHH... WELL, YOU SEE, I
THOUGHT WHEN HE GETS BACK HOME,
HE'D LIKE A LITTLE TASTE
OF THE HOLIDAY
AND I'D LIKE TO GIVE IT TO HIM,
IF YA KNOW WHAT I MEAN...
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU MEAN.
NOW WAIT! I DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING LIKE THAT, OKAY!
SO HENRIETTA, IS THERE
ANYONE OUT THERE
YOU'RE GIVING A PRESENT?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AH... AHEM...
WELL, NO. OF COURSE NOT.
YOU SURE?
[HENRIETTA]
SURE, I'M SURE!
GO BUY THE STUPID TREE ALREADY!
[MARIELLE]
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
EXCUSE ME!
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
IT'S A ONE‐SIDED LOVE
KEPT AT A SAFE DISTANCE,
FOR SURE.
IT'S BETTER TO
KEEP IT A SECRET
AND SIMPLY ENJOY THESE
SWEET FEELINGS ON MY OWN.
SOME DREAMS STAY UNFULFILLED,
BUT THAT'S ONLY NATURAL,
I THINK.
I CAN BEAR THE PAIN FOR NOW.
THAT'LL BE THE BEST
FOR BOTH OF US.
(MARIELLE GIGGLES)
[SERARA]
A LITTLE HELP HERE...
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
MARIELLE HAS A BEAUTIFUL
AND CHEERFUL ATTITUDE
THAT'S ALMOST INFECTIOUS.
SHE'S CONFIDENT AND POSITIVE.
I THINK THAT MUST BE
WHERE IT COMES FROM.
BUT AKATSUKI...
AKATSUKI IS DAZZLING!
[AKATSUKI] HM?
SHE HASN'T LOST THE
DELICATE FRAILTY OF YOUTH.
IT NORMALLY FADES SO QUICKLY.
SOFT AND TENDER SIDE SHE HAS
MIGHT BE A SHORTCOMING TO SOME,
BUT I SEE IT AS
A WONDERFUL ASSET.
ALTHOUGH I DOUBT
SHE REALIZES THAT...
GAH! I LOVE HER SO MUCH,
I COULD JUST WRAP MYSELF
AROUND HER AND SQUEEZE HER UP!
[AKATSUKI]
UH?
[RAYNESHIA]
THANKS FOR WAITING FOR ME!
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA, YOU LOOK SO
CUTE AND FLUFFY LIKE A SNOWBALL!
HOW NICE OF YOU.
SHE LET ME PICK IT
OUT OF HER WARDROBE.
COME ON! LET'S HEAD OUT!
[MARIELLE] WE SHOULD TAKE
A WALK AROUND TOWN
BEFORE WE HAVE THAT STEW.
I'D REALLY LIKE TO SHOW YOU
MORE ABOUT CHRISTMAS
WHILE WE HAVE THE TIME, NESSIE!
SURE!
(GIGGLE)
[HENRIETTA] BE CAREFUL!
THE SIDEWALK'S FROZEN, MARIELLE!
AH, AH, OHHHH!
[ALL] UH...
[MARIELLE] THAT HURTS... OOOOH
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
I REALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND
ADVENTURERS, THEY'RE JUST...
THEY'RE SO MUCH DIFFERENT
THAN WE ARE.
A LOT OF MY PEOPLE HAVE ASKED ME
QUESTIONS ABOUT THE ADVENTURERS,
AND TO BE TOTALLY HONEST,
I'M NOT SURE I HAVE ANY
HELPFUL ANSWERS.
I'VE SPENT A LOT OF TIME IN THIS
CITY OF THEIRS, AKIHABARA,
AND I THINK I'VE WOUND UP
BEING MORE CONFUSED
THAN WHEN I STARTED.
HOWEVER, THERE IS ONE THING
I HAVE LEARNED.
ADVENTURERS ARE
SIMPLY ADVENTURERS.
I MIGHT NOT KNOW
ALL THE ANSWERS,
BUT LABELLING THEM ISN'T
THE RIGHT PLACE TO START.
WE CAN'T LOOK AT THEM BASED
ON THE KIND OF WORK THEY DO.
I KNOW THAT MUCH.
ADVENTURERS ARE LIKE GEMSTONES.
EVERY ONE OF THEM IS
UNIQUE AND BEAUTIFUL;
AND EVERY ONE I'VE MET
HAS THEIR OWN INNER LIGHT.
THESE PEOPLE ARE SO SPECIAL.
I REALLY DON'T THINK I HAVE THE
RIGHT TO CALL THEM MY FRIENDS.
[RAYNESHIA]
HUH?
AH!
[MARIELLE]
WELL, LOOKIE THERE! WE'RE HERE!
[SERARA] I TELL YOU,
THE STEW HERE IS TO DIE FOR!
[RIEZE] I HEAR NO ONE HAS EVER
LEFT THIS PLACE UNSATISFIED.
[SERARA]
C'MON, LET'S GO IN!
[AKATSUKI]
I'M AFRAID I MUST BE GOING.
[ALL]
HUH?
[MARIELLE]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TAKE CARE OF.
UH... UM, OKAY.
IF YOU'RE SURE, WE'LL GO AHEAD
AND TAKE OVER FROM HERE.
MHM...
[RIEZE] SHE'S PROBABLY GOING TO
WATCH ANOTHER TRAINING SESSION.
I KNOW SOMETHING'S TROUBLING
HER, I WISH I COULD HELP...
SHE'S ALMOST LIKE
A SHARP DAGGER.
[HENRIETTA] HUH?
SHE'S LIKE A PURE
OBSIDIAN BLADE,
SO STRONG AND BEAUTIFUL.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
IT'S NOT LIKE JUST WATCHING
OTHER PEOPLE TRAIN WILL
HELP ME GET ANY STRONGER.
I DON'T HAVE THE POWER TO MAKE
ANYTHING WORK FOR ME,
THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
[AKATSUKI]
UH,
I WANT TO SEE MY LORD AGAIN...
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] JUST LET
ME SEE HIM FOR A MOMENT.
JUST LET ME TALK TO HIM.
I WANT TO BE NEAR HIM AGAIN.
I WANT THE TWO OF US
TO SIT ON THE SOFA
AND LOOK OUT THE WINDOW.
I WANT TO EAT
RED BEAN BUNS WITH HIM!
I WANT TO BE WITH
MY LORD FOREVER.
WE BELONG TOGETHER.
BUT I'M... ONLY FOOLING
MYSELF, AREN'T I?
HE'S NOT HERE.
SO I JUST HAVE TO WAIT FOR HIM.
AND THEN I'LL BE READY
TO FACE MY LORD AGAIN...
ACHOO!
[KYOKO, THINKING] I MANAGED
TO GET THREE SALTED SALMON
AT SHOPPING DISTRICT 8!
MASTER SOJIRO IS GONNA
LOVE THESE. I JUST KNOW IT!
HUH?
SANTA CLAUS?
[KYOKO, THINKING]
THAT'S NOT SANTA!
UH....
[KYOKO, THINKING]
THAT'S A PLAYER‐KILLER!
BUT, HE CAN'T DO ANYTHING
TO ME IN TOWN, CAN HE?!
[NERURESU, CHUCKLING]
THE ROYAL GUARDS AREN'T
COMING TO HELP YOU.
FINE BY ME!
[KYOKO, THINKING]
I'M NOT THE CAPTAIN OF
THE WEST WIND BRIGADE'S
SECOND UNIT FOR NOTHING.
I'M NOT DYING
IN THE STREET!
[NERURESU]
HEHE
(INHALE, EXHALE)
UH...
(LAUGH)
[KYOKO]
UH...
UGH!
(LABORED BREATH)
GUH...
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
SOJIRO SITS, QUIETLY SEETHING
WITH RAGE AFTER A
DEAR FRIEND WAS MURDERED.
RAYNESHIA IS FORCED TO
MAKE A GRAVE DECISION.
AND THE WEIGHT OF THE
PRINCESS' FEELINGS
ARE LEFT ON THE
SHOULDERS OF ANOTHER.
THE BATTLE AGAINST THE
SERIAL KILLER BEGINS AT LAST!
AND IN THE HEAT OF BATTLE,
SOJIRO REVEALS THE
SECRETS OF THE ORAL ARTS.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP, ONE MORE TIME!