(STREET NOISES)
[MAN A]
KEEP IT MOVING!
[MAN B] EIGHTEEN MORE
CASES OF EXP POTIONS!
[MIZPHA] HUMPH! THE GREED
OF THESE ADVENTURERS.
I HEARD NOW THEY'RE TRYING
TO BUILD A FLYING MACHINE.
FOR GOD'S SAKE, HOW MUCH
MORE DO THESE PEOPLE WANT?
[LOREILE] ALLOW
ME TO REMIND YOU
THAT OUR OWN PRINCESS NUREHA
IS AN ADVENTURER
AND SHE'S LENT THIS VERY TRAIN
TO THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
WORTH SOME CONSIDERATION.
[MIZPHA]
HMPH...
WHATEVER THE MASTER CAPTAIN
OF THE PALACE GUARD WISHES.
[KR] PULLING SECURITY AGAIN?
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK YOU
ACTUALLY LIKE THIS SCHLEP WORK.
SO WHERE'S THE PRINCESS?
[KAZUHIKO]
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
[KR]
STILL COOPED UP INSIDE, HUH?
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
INTIX HAS PLANNED
FOR OUR RELUCTANT NOBLEWOMAN?
[KAZUHIKO]
REPLACING KANAMI.
I'M NOT SO SURE JUST ANYONE
CAN FILL THOSE BIG SHOES
OF HERS YOU KNOW?
THAT'S TRUE.
[KAZUHIKO] IT'S BEEN TWO YEARS
SINCE THE TEA PARTY DISBANDED.
I'M NOT SO SURE SHE WAS ALL
THAT INTERESTED IN COMING BACK.
I DUNNO, YOU'D BE SURPRISED
WHO GOT CAUGHT IN HERE.
HUH?!
UH‐HUH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I RAN INTO HER WHEN I
WENT TO THE CHINA SERVER.
[KAZUHIKO] (GASP)
WAIT A MINUTE...
SHE STARTED PLAYING
ELDER TALES AGAIN.
[KR] GUESS SO...
AND LET ME TELL YOU MY FRIEND
SHE WAS PRETTY TERRIFYING!
SHE HASN'T CHANGED ONE
BIT SINCE THE LAST TIME.
SHE'S RESTED UP AND
READY TO DO SOME DAMAGE.
[KR, VOICEOVER]
RIGHT AFTER WE ALL WOKE UP HERE,
I DECIDED TO TAKE A
TRIP TO MAINLAND CHINA
TO SEE WHAT I COULD FIND
OUT ABOUT THIS PLACE.
I USED SOUL POSSESSION AND TOOK
COMMAND OF A HORSE'S BODY.
AND THEN, THERE THEY WERE...
[KANAMI]
(CLANG) OOOOHHHH!
THIS IS SO SWEET!
I HAVE STRUCK IT
RICH WITH ADVENTURE!
LET'S ROCK AND ROLL, FROGNARDO!
[LEONARDO]
IT'S LEONARDO, KANAMI! LEONARDO!
[KANAMI]
WOOHOO!
BANG! BOOM! POW! SLAM! WOOHOO!
(EXPLOSIONS)
[KR] 'COURSE, SHE WASN'T
ALL THAT DIFFICULT TO FIND.
[KANAMI]
WHOA! THEY JUST KEEP COMING!
[LEONARDO] YEAH, WELL
I TRIED TO WARN YOU!
THIS IS A RAID‐RANKED EVENT!
[COPPELIA] 2000 DAYLIGHT
SHADES IN THE AREA.
[KANAMI] SO DEATH WARPS AND
RETURN SPELLS
WON'T GET US OUTTA THIS ONE?
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS GUYS?
OH THIS IS SO EXCITING!
[ELIAS] UNFORTUNATELY I CAN'T
KILL ANYTHING
BECAUSE I'M STILL UNDER
THE FAIRY EYE'S CURSE.
[LEONARDO]
KINDA LAME, MY MAN.
[COPPELIA] THERE'S AN
OPENING IN THE BATTLEFIELD.
(ALL SURPRISED)
[LEONARDO]
WHAT IS THAT?!
[KANAMI]
WELL DON'T JUST STAND THERE,
HOP ALONG FROG‐BOY!
[LEONARDO]
MY NAME'S LEONARDO!
[ELIAS] WHY DO WE HAVE
TO GO ON FOOT ANYWAY?!
[KANAMI]
WHAT?! THAT'S REALLY YOU KR?
I THOUGHT THAT MAYBE ONE OF US
MUST'VE SUMMONED A HORSEY!
[KR] I SEE YOU'RE
THE SAME AS EVER...
I THOUGHT YOU GAVE UP THE GAME
FOR GOOD WHEN YOU LEFT JAPAN.
SO WHAT'S UP? WHAT HAPPENED?
[KANAMI] THEY'VE GOT COMPUTERS
IN OTHER COUNTRIES, YOU KNOW!
[KANAMI] AND WELL,
HERE WE ALL ARE!
[KR] OKAY, SO WHAT'RE YOU
DOING OUT HERE IN CHINA?
[KANAMI]
ME? I'M ON MY WAY BACK TO JAPAN!
[KR] WHAT? WHY WOULD
YOU GO BACK THERE?!
[ELIAS] UH, JAPAN'S
THE OTHER WAY.
[KANAMI] I HEARD THAT OVER
ON THE YAMATO SERVER
THEY'RE CALLING THIS WHOLE
PREDICAMENT THE "APOCALYPSE"
I REALLY WANT TO FIND
OUT WHAT CAUSED US ALL
TO GET PULLED INSIDE HERE.
[LEONARDO] I THINK IT'S
SAFE TO SAY IT HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH
NOVASPHERE PIONEERS.
[KR, VOICEOVER] WHEN THE
DEVELOPERS CREATED
THE TWELFTH EXPANSION PACK,
YOU HAVE TO WONDER
IF THIS WAS ALL PLANNED OR SOME
SORT OF HUGE ACCIDENT.
I DON'T KNOW BUT...
GOD ONLY KNOWS
HOW MANY PEOPLE
WERE LOGGED IN
WHEN THEY LAUNCHED THE
UPGRADE.
WHY SO MANY
JAPANESE?
[KR] YAMATO'S
FURTHEST TO THE EAST.
[KAZUHIKO]
WHAT?
THEY SCHEDULED
EVERY SERVER TO
COME BACK UP AT
MIDNIGHT ON MAY 3RD.
[KAZUHIKO] AH, SO THE REST OF
THE COUNTRIES DIDN'T COME UP
UNTIL EACH HOUR AFTERWARDS,
EXCEPT FOR INDIA AND KOREA.
[KR]
THERE YA GO.
EVEN IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE,
SHE MANAGED TO PUT
A PARTY TOGETHER.
[LEONARDO] AHHH... MAN
I MISS MEGAMEAT PIZZAS.
[KR, VOICEOVER] LEONARDO, THEIR
ASSASSIN, WAS PULLED OUT OF
THE AMERICAN SERVER WHEN
HE USED A FAIRY RING.
NOW HE'S STUCK HERE, TOO.
HE HAD JUST JOINED THE
PARTY WHEN I FOUND HER.
[COPPELIA] WOULD YOU LIKE
TO BE HEALED, LEONARDO?
[KR, VOICEOVER]
KANAMI MANAGED TO FIND COPPELIA,
THE CLERIC IN HER GROUP,
WHILE SNOOPING AROUND.
[LEONARDO] NOPE... I'M JUST
JONESIN' FOR A PIZZA PIE.
[KR, VOICEOVER] AND THEN THERE'S
THE SWORDSMAN ELIAS HACKBLADE.
[KAZUHIKO, VOICEOVER] WHAT? AS
IN THE ANCIENT ELIAS HACKBLADE?!
[KR, VOICEOVER] THERE
ARE 13 ORDER OF CHIVALRY
THAT MAINTAIN PEACE
ACROSS THE LAND.
HE BELONGS TO THE KNIGHTS
OF THE RED BRANCH.
NOT ONLY IS THIS
GUY A BLADE‐MANCER,
HE'S ALSO A NOBLE OF
ANCIENT OF THE BLUE BLOOD.
I MEAN THIS GUY'S ON THE
COVER OF THE ELDER TALES
MANUAL FOR GOD'S SAKE!
DIDN'T WE COME TO AGREE THAT
ALL THE ANCIENTS WERE GONE?
AND NO ONE'S EVER SEEN THE
IZUMO KNIGHTS BACK IN YAMATO.
SO TELL ME THIS, WHAT
WOULD A GUY LIKE THAT
BE DOING RUNNING
AROUND WITH KANAMI?
[KR] WELL, IT IS KANAMI.
[KAZUHIKO] GOOD POINT.
ANYWAY, WE MOVED ON AND
CONTINUED OUR JOURNEY.
(SCREAMS)
[KR] AND WE FOUND SOMETHING...
[KANAMI]
WOHOA...
OOF! WAAUGH!
HEY! NOW WHY'D YOU HAVE
TO GO AND DO THAT?!
[LEONARDO]
MPH. WHAT'S IN THERE, KANAMI?!
[KANAMI] UH... A BOY. I THINK...
[LEONARDO] WHOA, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH HIS STATUS BAR...?
DUDE. WHAT THE HELL IS HE?!
[KANAMI] NOW DON'T YOU
HURT HIM, FROGNARDO!
[LEONARDO] HELLO! HE IS
TRYING TO EAT US! UWAH!
(SNARLING)
(SNARL)
[LEONARDO] HUH?
(CONCERNED GASPS)
(GROWLING)
HUH?
(SEJIN SNARLING)
[LEONARDO]
ELIAS! DON'T LET HIM GET AWAY!
[ELIAS] YOU GOT IT! HAHHH!
I CALL UPON THE BLACK
NIGHT FAIRY'S ARM!
NIGHT SPLASH!
[SEJIN] RAGGGHHHHH!
WELL DON'T OVER‐DO IT.
SORRY.
(THUD)(GASPS)
[LEONARDO]
COPPELIA! LOOK OUT!
(SNARLING)
[LEONARDO, THINKING] HE'S A
PERSON OF THE LAND. HE'S AN NPC.
I COULD USE ASSASSINATE AND GET
THIS OVER WITH IN SECONDS!
WOULDN'T BE A BIG DEAL. HE'S
JUST A PROGRAM, RIGHT?
[LEONARDO] UGH!
(GROWLING)
(KANAMI GASPS)
(SEJIN SNARLS)
[KANAMI]
FROGGY?!
[LEONARDO]
DON'T WORRY;
I USED PARALYZING BLOW.
JUST NEEDED TO STOP
ALL THIS NONSENSE.
[ELIAS] MISTRESS KANAMI, DID
YOU NOTICE SOMETHING STRANGE?
IT WAS LIKE THE BOY
HAD TWO STATUS BARS.
[LEONARDO] DOES ANYONE
KNOW WHAT THAT WAS ABOUT?
[KANAMI] HAS THIS EVER
HAPPENED TO ANYONE
IN YOUR VILLAGE BEFORE?
[YAGUDO]
YES. ONE MOMENT SOMEONE'S FINE.
AND THE NEXT THEY'RE ATTACKING
PEOPLE LIKE A RABID ANIMAL.
IT HAS EVERYONE SCARED TO DEATH.
THE VILLAGERS HAVE BEEN CALLING
THE SICKNESS "YIGUI,"
BUT WE DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
MAKING IT HAPPEN. (BOY SHUDDERS)
[KANAMI] IT'S ALL SO
MYSTERIOUS, YOU KNOW.
[SHIROE] WE CAN MAKE IT HAPPEN!
[KANAMI] HM?
[SHIROE] EVERYONE'S GOT TO PUT
IN THE WORK TO SEE
THAT NEW SUNRISE.
AND I KINDA GET THE FEELING YOU
REALLY WANT TO SEE IT,
DON'T YOU? (KANAMI
LETS OUT SMALL LAUGH)
[ELIAS] I HEARD YOU HAVE
MERCHANTS COMING
TO THE VILLAGE IN A FEW DAYS.
[COPPELIA] THEY MIGHT HAVE THE
CONSUMABLES WE NEED
AND POSSIBLY SOME INFORMATION.
[KR] WE SHOULD PROBABLY WAIT
FOR THE MERCHANTS TO GET HERE.
[KANAMI]
DEFINITELY.
(ANNOYED)
[BOY A]
HEY, MISTER!
[GIRL A]
WHAT'RE YOU ALL GREEN FOR?
[BOY B]
YEAH! YOU LOOK LIKE A BIG FROG!
[LEONARDO]
SURE! FROGS ARE HEROIC!
NINJA FROGS ARE WARRIORS ‐
AND THE ULTIMATE SYMBOL OF
BRAVERY ALL OVER THE WORLD!
[BOY D]
YOU LOOK FUNNY!
[BOY B] YEAH, I DON'T THINK SO.
[BOY C] FROGGIES JUMP!
[LEONARDO] JESUS CHRIST, FORGOT
HOW MUCH I HATE FRICKIN' KIDS.
[LEONARDO, THINKING] I
BETTER HOLD IT TOGETHER.
IF I START WAILING ON A BUNCH
OF LITTLE CHILDREN
I'M GONNA LOOK LIKE A D‐BAG.
I JUST HEARD A MARE CAME
ONTO YOU IN THE BARN, KR!
[KR] (SHARP BREATH)
WHO TOLD YOU THAT!
[KANAMI] ARE YOU A STUDLY STUD?
[KR] OH SHUT UP!
[KANAMI] SO, HOW ARE
THINGS OVER IN JAPAN?
I BETCHA GOT A LOT OF
STORIES TO SHARE BY NOW!
[KANAMI]
HUH?! SHIROE DID WHAT?
[KR] APPARENTLY HE'S THE CENTRAL
FIGURE IN AN ORGANIZATION
KNOWN AS THE ROUND
TABLE CONFERENCE.
BUT FOR WHATEVER REASON,
SOMEONE ELSE SERVES AS THE
OFFICIAL REPRESENTATIVE.
[KANAMI] (GIGGLE) LOOKS LIKE
MY TOUR GUIDE'S MOVING UP!
[SHIROE]
EHMMMM! (SHUDDERING)
IS EVERYTHING ALL
RIGHT, MY LORD?
I GUESS... IT JUST
KINDA FELT LIKE
SOMEONE DROPPED THE WEIGHT OF
THE ENTIRE WORLD
ON MY SHOULDERS.
(GRUNT)
[LEONARDO, THINKING]
BEFORE WE GOT PULLED IN HERE
I WAS NEVER ABLE TO
USE MORE THAN
ONE FIGHTING SKILL AT A TIME.
BUT NOW THAT I CAN ACTIVATE THE
SKILLS WITH MY OWN BODY,
I CAN QUEUE UP CONSECUTIVE
MOVES BEFORE I EVEN USE THEM!
[LEONARDO]
(PANTING) HEY COPPELIA.
[COPPELIA] LEONARDO, YOU
COULD USE SOME HEALING.
[LEONARDO] UH, NAH. I'M FINE.
(HEAVY BREATHS)
[LEONARDO] SO, TELL ME...
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
THE EXPANSION PACK?
[COPPELIA] THE ONLY THING
COPPELIA HAS HEARD IS
THAT IT WAS LAUNCHED
ON THE YAMATO SERVER.
[LEONARDO] OK, SO WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF GOING
OVER TO THE YAMATO SERVER?
MISTRESS KANAMI WOULD
LIKE TO GO THERE...
AND SO COPPELIA WILL BE MAKING
IT THE HIGHEST PRIORITY.
SO WHAT'S YOUR "MISTRESS
KANAMI'S" DEAL ANYWAY? UH?
[COPPELIA] COPPELIA'S
MISTRESS... IS LIKE... THE DAWN.
[LEONARDO]
HUH?
[COPPELIA] RIGHT NOW...
THE SUN IS RACING...
IT'S HIDING BEHIND THE SKY.
AND THERE IT HAS BEEN, ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THE WORLD...
BUT TOMORROW AT 04:38, LIGHT
WILL FILL THE EASTERN SKY.
AT NIGHT, THE SKY IS
FILLED WITH DARKNESS.
A DARK PURPLE BEGINS TO COLOR
THE EAST ‐ SLOWLY, CALMLY.
NEXT, THE PURPLE
GRADUALLY LIFTS...
AND THEN, IT TURNS TO BLUE.
YET, THERE IS STILL NO LIGHT,
EVEN AS THE SHADES SPREAD.
IT CAN'T BE SEEN, BUT ITS
PRESENCE GUIDES US ALL.
AND IT IS THIS GLOWING BLUE
PROMISE OF DAWN
THAT KEEPS PEOPLE
FROM GIVING UP.
AND MY MISTRESS... IS
THAT GLOWING PROMISE.
(EXHALE)
[KR] NOW LET'S JUMP
AHEAD A FEW DAYS...
SURE ENOUGH, THE MERCHANT
CARAVAN STROLLED INTO TOWN.
HOWEVER...
[CHUNG LU]
YOU MAY REFER TO ME AS CHUNG LU.
I AM A PERSONAL BODYGUARD
AFFILIATED WITH
THE LELANG CANINE CAVALRY.
UNFORTUNATELY... WE WERE
AMBUSHED. I WAS ISOLATED...
AND I WAS UNABLE TO FEND
OFF THE ATTACKERS.
[KANAMI]
OH?
[ELIAS]
SO TELL US. WHAT HAPPENED?
[RASPHIA] INSIGNIFICANT PAWNS.
THEY'LL GET THE FATE
THEY DESERVE.
[PAPS] EVERY WORLD DEMANDS
WEAKLINGS FALL ASIDE.
[CHUNG LU]
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY.
NORMALLY WE WOULD HAVE
ESCORTED THIS CARAVAN
SAFELY TO IT'S DESTINATION.
[KANAMI] OH NO, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT. I THINK WE WERE ALL
HEADING IN THE SAME
DIRECTION, ANYWAY.
[CHUNG LU, THINKING] EVER SINCE
THE APOCALYPSE OCCURRED...
THE LELANG CANINE CAVALRY
HAS BEEN FINDING WORK
AS A BODYGUARD AGENCY
FOR TRAVELING NPCS.
[CHUNG LU]
I DO APOLOGIZE.
[JUHA]
NOBODY'S BLAMING YOU FOR IT!
YOU WERE OUTNUMBERED OUT THERE!
[CHUNG LU]
BUT I...
I MEAN... WE CAN ALWAYS
COME BACK TO LIFE!
WE'RE ADVENTURERS...
[LEONARDO]
OKAY, FINE,
SO A FEW NPCS BIT THE
DUST ALONG THE WAY.
THEY'RE DATA. NO BIGGIE.
[KR] DIDN'T YOU SAY THE
LELANG CANINE CAVALRY IS
GOING TO EXTERMINATE
A HORDE OF GNOLLS?
[CHUNG LU] RIGHT. THEY'RE
GOING IN WITH 96 PLAYERS.
A TRUE LEGION RAID. 4 PARTIES.
THE GNOLLS ARE IN THE PILLAR
RUINS OF TONE'S GRAVE.
AND THAT'S WHERE THE PARTY'S
HEADED. OVER 4000 STRONG.
[LEONARDO] HEY, AS LONG AS YOUR
GUYS ARE ALL LEVEL 90 OR BETTER,
THEN THEY SHOULDN'T HAVE
ANY PROBLEM, RIGHT?
[KANAMI, THINKING]
GOD, I'M SO JEALOUS!
I WANNA BE IN A FIGHT LIKE THAT!
[RASPHIA] WE MUST NOT LEAVE
THE CORRIDOR TO HEAVEN AGAPE.
IT'S TOO MUCH FUN
TO SEE THEIR TORMENT
OF NOT KNOWING WHAT'S TO COME!
[PAPS] LET THEIR
DEATHS BE SWIFT!
(SURPRISED)
[LEONARDO]
THEY GOT WIPED OUT?!
[CHUNG LU] THE ENTIRE LEGION
WAS CUT DOWN LIKE DOGS.
ON TOP OF THAT, A NEW GROUP OF
MONSTERS WITH TWO STATUS BARS
WERE SPOTTED, ALONG
WITH A BLACK DRAGON.
[COPPELIA]
THE PARALLEL ONES...
[KR] KANAMI!
[ALL] HM?
[KR] A HORDE OF GNOLLS ARE
ADVANCING TOWARD THE NEXT ZONE.
SOMEWHERE AROUND 500 OF THEM!
(KANAMI GASPS)
[KR] AND FROM THE LOOKS OF IT,
THEY'RE GONNA END UP HITTING THE
VILLAGE WHERE WE JUST STAYED!
[LEONARDO] I THOUGHT GNOLLS ONLY
HUNG OUT IN CAVES AND RUINS.
[LEONARDO, THINKING] THEY'RE
ONLY SUPPOSED TO ATTACK
IF YOU MESS WITH 'EM!
[KR] YEAH, WELL!
SOMETHING'S GOT 'EM ALL RILED
UP AND LOOKING FOR DINNER!
[KANAMI]
AWESOME! AWESOME!
FIVE HUNDRED GUARDS MEANS
ONE HECK OF A TREASURE!
I COULD NEVER HAVE FUN LIKE
THIS IN THE REAL WORLD!
NOT EVEN CLOSE!
[LEONARDO]
WHAT?
NOW THIS IS THE FIGHT
I WAS LOOKING FOR!
I'VE STRUCK IT RICH IN COMBAT!
[LEONARDO]
WHAT?!
[KANAMI] THIS IS AN OPPORTUNITY
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO PASS UP!
[KR] WAIT. YOU'RE SERIOUSLY
CONSIDERING GOING DOWN
TO TONE'S GRAVE AND
TAKING ON 500 GNOLLS?!
[KANAMI] WAY TO GO, KR!
I'M GLAD YOU GET IT!
(KR WHINNIES)
[LEONARDO] ARE YOU CRAZY?!
[LEONARDO]
DIDN'T YOU JUST HEAR THAT
THE LEGION RAID GOT THEIR
ASSES HANDED TO 'EM?
[KANAMI] THAT'S BECAUSE THEY
WENT IN WITHOUT SCOUTING IT.
WE'RE GONNA GATHER INFO... AND
WE'RE NOT GONNA PICK A FIGHT.
AND WHEN THEY LEAVE,
WE'RE GONNA RUN INSIDE
AND KILL THE BIG BOSS!
IT'LL BE A PERFECT GAME!
WE'LL BE THE CHAMPIONS
OF THE UNIVERSE!
[LEONARDO] UH?
[KR] DO WE EVEN HAVE ANY INTEL?
[KANAMI] THINK ABOUT
EVERYTHING CHUNG LU TOLD US!
[KR] HUH? HOW IS THAT
SUPPOSED TO HELP?
[KANAMI] YOU'RE THE STRATEGIST,
KR. FIGURE IT OUT!
(WHINNY) [LEONARDO]
OH MAN. THERE IS NO WAY!
[KANAMI] LOOK, IT REALLY ISN'T A
MATTER OF WHETHER WE CAN
OR WHETHER WE CAN'T GET IT DONE.
[LEONARDO]
THEN WHAT IS IT?!
(GIGGLE)
[KANAMI]
WE JUST NEED TO BE THERE, OKAY?
[LEONARDO] AND WHY DO WE
"NEED" TO BE THERE?
[KANAMI] (INHALE) YOU ALREADY
KNOW. AND YOU DON'T NEED TO ASK.
[LEONARDO]
HUH?
WHY IN GOD'S NAME SHOULD WE RISK
OUR NECKS FOR A BUNCH OF NPCS?
[ELIAS] I'M WITH KANAMI ON THIS
ONE. [LEONARDO] UH...!
[ELIAS] I'M NOT SAYING THIS OUT
OF SOME SENSE OF DEBT TO HER.
I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN AN ANCIENT.
FROM THE FOUNDING DAYS OF THE
THIRTEEN ORDERS OF CHIVALRY.
IT HAS BEEN MY SWORN DUTY
TO PROTECT THEM.
(GIGGLE)(CLINK)
[LEONARDO, THINKING] YEAH,
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S NOT A PLAYER.
HE'S PART OF THE GAME!
BUT LIKE SOME SORT OF
SOUPED‐UP PERSON OF THE LAND!
[ELIAS]
WHAT ABOUT THE VILLAGERS?
[KANAMI] CHUNG LU, CAN
YOU WARN THEM FOR US?
[CHUNG LU] I'M ON IT.
[COPPELIA] COPPELIA WILL ALSO
ACCOMPANY HER MISTRESS.
WE CAN'T BEAT 500
GNOLLS, COPPELIA!
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU OWE THESE
PEOPLE ANYTHING, YOU KNOW! HUH?
COPPELIA IS NOT A PLAYER, BUT
STILL COMPELLED TO DO THIS.
[COPPELIA] A MONEY‐LAUNDERING
GROUP FROM CHINA
PROGRAMMED MMO
GOLD‐FARMING BOTS...
THEIR PURPOSE WAS TO ENRICH
THEIR MASTERS AND NOT CONSIDER
THEMSELVES. COPPELIA WAS ONE
SUCH BOT.
(GASP)
(HORSE WHINNY)
WHY AREN'T YOU OUT THERE
BEING ALL HEROIC N' STUFF?
[KR] I WAS KINDA CURIOUS
ABOUT SOMETHING.
[KR] WHAT DID, UH, COPPELIA
HAVE TO SAY TO YOU?
[LEONARDO] (SIGH) THAT SHE
WAS CREATED IN THE GAME...
JUST A FARMING BOT.
SOMETHING THAT PLAYS THE
GAME FOR SOMEONE ELSE.
SHE'S JUST ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE.
[COPPELIA]
TODAY'S ACTIVITY.
COPPELIA SUMMARY: HEALED
A TOTAL OF 18 PEOPLE,
BLESSED ANOTHER 49.
WHETHER OR NOT IT WAS HELPFUL
CANNOT BE OFFICIALLY DETERMINED.
COPPELIA DID RECEIVE VERBAL
INDICATION
FROM MANY OF THE ASSISTED.
COPPELIA WAS THANKED AND
APPRECIATED.
THIS OCCURRED 319 TIMES,
BUT THIS IS NOT THE SAME THING.
DID ANY OF IT HELP...?
DID I HELP?
[LEONARDO, THINKING]
SO HOW WOULD "THEY" HANDLE THIS?
MY MOST MAGNIFICENT
NINJA HEROES...
(EXHALE)
[LEONARDO]
YEAH I KNOW...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I WAS DOING
SITTING AROUND EITHER.
I'M GOING.
[KR]
OKAY? NOW I'M INTERESTED.
LET ME FRESHEN UP A BIT.
HUH?
[LEONARDO]
WAIT A SEC, YOU'RE KR?
PRETTY QUICK, AREN'TCHA?
[LEONARDO]
OKAY, I GIVE.
WHY THE HECK WERE YOU A HORSE?
(KR CRACKING BONES)
IT'S A LITTLE TRANS‐POSITIONING
SPELL CALLED CASTLING.
SUMMONERS USUALLY USE
IT IN AN EMERGENCY
TO SWITCH PLACES WITH A BEAST
THAT'S BEEN SUMMONED
AS A COMPANION.
[LEONARDO] WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
[KR] IT MEANS THAT I JUST
TRANSFERRED OVER TO
THIS SERVER FROM JAPAN. (EXHALE)
AND I'M JOINING THE PARTY!
[LEONARDO] WHY?
[KR] IT MIGHT SEEM
A LITTLE CRAZY...
BUT I RECOGNIZED YOUR OUTFIT.
I WAS PRETTY BIG FAN OF THE
SHOW BACK IN THE REAL WORLD.
[LEONARDO]
NHH? REALLY?
[KR] I SAY TO MYSELF,
"IF THAT FROG NINJA'S GONNA
SHOW OFF WHAT HE'S GOT
THEN I'M NOT GONNA JUST SIT
AROUND AND WATCH.
I GOTTA GET IN THERE AND BATTLE
FOR TRUTH AND JUSTICE?!
AWAKEN, MY FRIEND,
THE CRIMSON DRAGON!
RISE FROM THY GARNET SLUMBER...
AND DANCE IN THE SKIES!
(ROAR)
(BATTLE CRY)
(EXPLOSIONS)
[ELIAS] O FAIRY OF PUREST
WATER...
BECOME A BLADE 10,000‐FEET LONG
AND SHINE! COMPANION...! HWAH!
AQUA THOUSAND RAIN!
[KANAMI]
BAH! LA! HAHAA!
(PUNCHING GRUNTS)
[KANAMI]
UWUH?
LEONARDO?
[KR]
I CAN SEE TONE'S GRAVE!
[LEONARDO]
HANG ON.
[KR] LOOK AT THAT!
(ROAR)
[KR] WHOA...
I BET THAT THING IS RAID‐CLASS
OR EVEN DOUBLE‐RAID CLASS.
[LEONARDO] MUST BE THE BLACK
DRAGON
THAT CHUNG LU TOLD US ABOUT.
[KR] LOOK IT'S GOT RIDERS!
[LEONARDO] YOU THINK
THEY'RE BEHIND THIS?
[LEONARDO, VOICEOVER]
MUST MAKE THEM THE BOSSES.
[RASPHIA] WELL, WELL...
MORE MEDDLING ADVENTURERS.
[PAPS] THEY'RE NOTHING
BUT EMPTY SHELLS!
[LEONARDO]
HYAHHHH! (BREATH)
(ROAR) [LEONARDO] IF I CAN FIND
A WAY TO TAKE THE BOSSES OUT,
YOU THINK YOU'D BE ABLE TO
LURE THAT BLACK DRAGON AWAY!
[KR]
YEAH!
[LEONARDO]
ALL RIGHT!
COWABUNGA!
[KR?] DID HE JUST
SAY "COWABUNGA"?
[KANAMI] WOW! FROGNARDO'S
TOTALLY AWESOME!
(TUMBLING NOISES AND GRUNTS)
[ELIAS] LET'S GO!
(ALL TAKING OFF)
[RASPHIA]
LOOK AT YOU!
I'VE FOUND MYSELF AT
A RARE LOSS FOR WORDS!
[LEONARDO] YOU GOTTA
BE FRICKIN' KIDDING ME?
[LEONARDO, THINKING] RASPHIA,
LEVEL 89.
AT LEAST THIS ONE'S
GOT A NORMAL RANK.
(SURPRISED)
[KANAMI] PAPS, LEVEL 89.
ANOTHER NORMAL RANK HERE.
[PAPS] CHILD, YOU WERE
ABLE TO READ MY NAME.
LITERACY IS A SPECIAL
GIFT IN THIS WORLD, YES?
[ELIAS] THIS WORLD...?
SO HE'S A GENIUS?!
[PAPS] YOU'RE FAMILIAR
WITH US, SURVIVOR?
THEN YOU SHALL LIVE NO LONGER.
[KANAMI]
ELIAS!
(YELLS, SCREAMS)
[KANAMI]
EWW! IT'S ALL MUSHY AND GROSS!
(ROAR)
(SNARLS AND ROARS)
[PAPS] YOU ARE WITH A MOST
UNUSUAL PARTY, ANCIENT.
IT IS MY DUTY TO ENSURE EACH
OF YOU ARE PROPERLY DISPOSED OF.
[RASPHIA](LAUGHTER) JUST LOVELY!
THIS IS SUCH A DELIGHT! HMMM...
[LEONARDO]
UWAH! SHUT UP!
(LAUGH)
[LEONARDO, THINKING] SHE MUST
BE ONE OF THOSE PARALLELS!
BY FLIPPING HER STATUS BAR
FROM ONE NAME TO ANOTHER,
SHE CAN CONTROL HOW MUCH
DAMAGE SHE TAKES!
[LEONARDO, THINKING] PLUS,
SHE'S DUMPING ANY CHARACTERS
THAT'VE TAKEN TOO MUCH DAMAGE.
OKAY, YOU LITTLE FREAK,
I CAN STILL TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF YOUR CHARGE TIMES!
(GASP)
[LEONARDO] PARALLEL PLOT!
(RASPHIA GRUNTS)
[RASPHIA] WHAT'S THIS?
PAIN IS SUCH AN UNFAMILIAR
FEELING FOR ME.
[RASPHIA, THINKING] CRIMSON
BEYOND THE SETTING SUN!
RED DEEPER THAN
HURRICANE LILIES!
[LEONARDO]
HAHHHHHHHHH!
[RASPHIA, THINKING] SCARLET
TRUER THAN A ROSE! (LAUGHTER)
[PAPS]
POOR MISGUIDED ANCIENT...
[ELIAS]
THAT'S ENOUGH!
[PAPS]
HAVE ALL YOUR COMRADES FALLEN?
[ELIAS]
I TOLD YOU TO SHUT UP!
[PAPS]
I KNOW YOU ALL TOO WELL.
THE ANCIENTS‐NO, ALL
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
ARE NOTHING BUT AUTOMATONS!
[PAPS] YOU HAVE NO
WILL OF YOUR OWN.
SIMPLY WHAT IS WRITTEN
INTO YOUR SCRIPT!
YOU'RE A PRODUCT, CREATED
ONLY TO BE DESTROYED!
[ELIAS, THINKING]
THE FAIRIES, THEY AREN'T REAL.
AND THE ANCIENTS OR THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND... AH!
IT'S ALL A FANTASY...
[PAPS] AND AS SUCH, YOU ARE
MEANT TO BE FORGOTTEN
ONCE YOU ARE GONE.
YOU ARE BORN FROM NOTHING,
YOUR TIMELINE FROZEN,
YOU RETURN TO NOTHING!
[KANAMI] YEAH, WELL I
DON'T THINK SO! HWAH!
(ELIAS GASPS)
[KANAMI] DO YOU HEAR ME?!
ELI'S ALWAYS GONNA BE RIGHT HERE
WITH ME! YOU UNDERSTAND?!
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF PLANS!
AND WE'RE GONNA BE IN THIS
TOGETHER FOR A LONG LONG TIME!
SO YOU CAN JUST KEEP YOUR
CREEPY LITTLE TENTACLES
OFF, YOU GOT ME?!
[KR, VOICEOVER] GRANTED, I'M NOT
QUITE SURE ABOUT THE DETAILS
OF HOW THEY GOT OUTTA THAT.
[KAZUHIKO] WORRYING ABOUT HER
IS A BIG WASTE OF TIME, ANYWAY.
GUESS SHE REALLY HASN'T
CHANGED AT ALL.
I TOLD YOU! SHE'S JUST AS
CRAZY AS SHE ALWAYS WAS.
(SURPRISED)
[MAN D] PRINCESS NUREHA!
(MURMURS)
[INTIX] GO AHEAD
AND GIVE THEM WHAT
THEY'RE ASKING FOR,
"YOUR MAJESTY."
[MAN E] WHOA! IT'S
REALLY THE PRINCESS!
[WOMAN C] PRINCESS NUREHA!
[INTIX, THINKING]
HMPH! JUST KEEP IT UP.
SMILE YOU'RE PRETTY
LITTLE SMILE AND
GIVE THE RABBLE SOME HOPE. AFTER
ALL, IT'S ALL THEY'RE GONNA GET.
[KAZUHIKO] HAVE YOU TOLD
INTIX ANYTHING ABOUT THIS?
[KR] NUH‐UH. NO WAY.
FAR AS I KNOW,
SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW KANAMI
STARTED PLAYING AGAIN.
(ANNOYED)
HMPH.
YOU KNOW IT'S GONNA BE SOMETHIN'
WHEN THEY FINALLY RUN
INTO EACH OTHER, HUH?
(SIGH)
(CHEERING)
[SORCERER A]
MAGIC CIRCLES ARE READY.
[SORCERER B] RAILWAY MODS ARE
SET. BY YOUR COMMAND, MILADY.
[MIZPHA]
IT'S TIME TO GO TO WAR PEOPLE.
AND IT BEGINS IN THE EAST!
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
IT IS AN OBJECT OF DESIRE
AMONG INEXPERIENCED PLAYERS.
ANYTHING AND EVERYTHING CAN
FIT INSIDE "THE MAGIC BAG."
MINORI AND THE OTHER JUNIOR
MEMBERS ARE GOING ON
A QUEST TO CREATE THEIR OWN.
A NEW AND UNDISCOVERED WORLD
AWAITS THEM AS THEIR HEARTS
SWELL WITH FEAR AND
ANTICIPATION.
THEIR CARRIAGE IS PACKED
TIGHT, WITH HOPES AND DREAMS.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.