(ROAR)
HEH. COME ON YOU GUYS!
DON'T LET UP ON ME!
I NEED EVERYTHING YOU GOT!
NOW TAKE HIM DOWN!
GETTING A WIN AND SOLVING THE
PROBLEM AREN'T THE SAME.
[KANAMI]
WOOHOO!
BANG! BOOM! POW! SLAM! WOOHOO!
[NAOTSUGU]
FORTRESS STANCE!
I THINK I'M GOING TO TEST
OUT THESE NEW WEAPONS...
BY TAKING OFF YOUR HEAD!
[SOJIRO] WATCH CAREFULLY
AND LISTEN TO ME.
YOU MUST MAINTAIN AN ATTITUDE
OF CONSTANT IMPROVEMENT.
AND NEVER FOR A MOMENT DISCOUNT
TRAINING YOU'VE RECEIVED.
THIS IS IT! SHIROE, I NEED A
DISTRACTION FROM YOUR TEAM!
[KANAMI]
AWESOME, AWESOME!
FIVE HUNDRED GUARDS MEANS
ONE HECK OF A TREASURE!
I COULD NEVER HAVE FUN
LIKE THIS IN THE REAL WORLD.
NOT EVEN CLOSE!
I SEE IT NOW!
[SHIROE]
WILLIAM!
A LITTLE HELP HERE!
I CAN'T BEGIN TO TELL YOU HOW
GOOD MY DINNER'S GONNA BE...
AFTER I GET DONE
KICKING ALL YOUR BUTTS!
(GRUNTING)
HEY PEOPLE, GOT YOUR
PUMPKINS OVER HERE!
(CHEERING)
[MAN 1]
FOR LADY MISA
[CROWD]
D. D. D.!
[MAN 2]
THANKS COMMANDER TAKAYAMA!
OOOOOH! I WANNA PLAY!
YOU OUGHTA KNOW BY NOW THAT
ORGANIZERS HAVE TO WORK, BABY!
UWAH...
(CHUCKLING)
[MARIELLE]
OH COME ON!
I WANNA PLAY TUG OF WAR!
[NYANTA]
HMM. SO TELL ME.
WHY EXACTLY DID WE NEED TO HAVE
AN AFTER HALLOWEEN EVENT, HRMM?
[MARIELLE]
WELL, YOU REMEMBER THE EVENT
WE HAD FOR HALLOWEEN, RIGHT?
THAT'S KINDA WHY I WAS ASKING...
THE GAME DEVELOPERS ALREADY HAVE
AN EVENT THIS TIME OF YEAR,
MONSTERS DROP PUMPKINS
WHEN THEY'RE BEATEN
DURING THE LAST THREE DAYS
OF THE MONTH, YOU DIG?
AND THAT'S JUST IT!
WE'VE GOT A BUNCH OF PRIZE
PUMPKINS RIGHT HERE!
SO WHY NOT HAVE AN EVENT TO
FIND A WAY TO GIVE 'EM AWAY?
COUNT ON MARIELLE, THE PARTY
STRATEGIST, TO MAKE IT WORK!
[NYANTA]
NICE AIR GLASSES, GIRL.
[NYANTA] ONE THING'S FOR SURE.
(STRUGGLED GRUNTS)
[MARIELLE] HM?
[NYANTA] THIS CITY OF OURS HAS
BECOME A SMOOTH PLACE TO LIVE.
[MARIELLE]
YES IT HAS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW FAST IT HAS HAPPENED.
IT SEEMS LIKE JUST YESTERDAY
THAT WE GOT TRAPPED HERE
IN ELDER TALES.
I MEAN WE'VE STARTED A CITY,
SET UP A SYSTEM,
AND PUT TOGETHER
THE ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE
ALL IN A VERY SHORT
PERIOD OF TIME.
YOU KNOW IT, AND EVERYONE'S
PUT IN A LOT OF WORK
TO MAKE THIS HAPPEN,
EVEN LITTLE SERARA.
[SMASH] DON'T USE YOUR HANDS!
AND REMEMBER...
YOU GOTTA PAY FOR EVERY BUN
YOUR DROP OUT THERE!
EH! MMPH! EHH!
[SERARA, THINKING] I'M GOING TO
BEAT EVERYONE TO WIN THIS RACE
AND THEN I'M GONNA HAVE A
PUMPKIN PARTY WITH MISTER CAT!
(CHEERING)
JUST LOOK AT TOYA AND MINORI.
TOYA! YOU CAN'T DO
THIS WITH JUST ATTITUDE
ANTICIPATE WHERE
THE PHANTOM'S GOING!
GOT IT! OKAY! I CAN
TOTALLY DO THIS!
[NYANTA] ISUZU AND RUDY
ARE IN THE THICK OF IT, HMM?
[SMASH] ARE YOU READY?
DO ANY OF THESE
WANNABES‐NAY‐WHOS
THINK THEY CAN
ACTUALLY BEAT US?
AFTER ALL, OUR TEAMWORK
IS AMAZING,
AND OUR FOOTWORK IS NOTHING
SHORT OF MAGNIFICENT!
[SMASH]GET SET!
(HORN BLOWS)
RUDY! THEY'RE
STARTING WITHOUT US!
OH, COME ON!
(CROWD CHEERING)
WOW! I'VE NEVER SEEN AN
OBSTACLE COURSE LIKE THIS!
INCREDIBLY DONE!
THAT'S AKATSUKI
FOR YOU!
AMAZING!
FIRST PLACE GOES TO
AKATSUKI OF LOG HORIZON!
HEHE. I WILL MAKE SURE WE TAKE
HOME THE GRAND PRIZE, MY LORD!
[MINORI] MISS AKATSUKI!
[RUDY] (LAUGHING) WOOO!
[TOYA] THAT WAS REALLY SUPER,
MISS AKATSUKI!
[ISUZU] YEAH! YOU WERE GREAT!
(CHEERING) WOO!
I JUST WISH SHIROE AND NAOTSUGU
COULD BE OUT HERE TODAY!
I KNOW WHAT YOU
MEAN, BABY.
THEY'RE STILL HUNG UP
WITH THE NEGOTIATIONS.
[MARIELLE]
WELL, THAT'S A SHAME!
[NYANTA] MHMM!
[HENRIETTA] AH...
THE ARMOR'S EMPTY.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, YEAH. SO
THERE'S NO ONE IN THERE,
BUT THEY'RE STILL
ROYAL GUARD ARMOR, RIGHT?
[HENRIETTA] AND THEY'RE STILL
NOT GOING TO DO ANYTHING
UNLESS YOU TRY PICKING A FIGHT
WITH SOMEONE IN A
NON‐COMBAT ZONE
[NAOTSUGU] JUST NEVER BEEN
THIS CLOSE TO 'EM
IT'S SURE TAKING SHIROE
A WHILE TO GET THIS DONE...
MAKES ME WONDER IF
EVERYTHING IS GOING OKAY...
[NAOTSUGU] IT'S BEEN KINDA
ROUGH IN THERE FOR HIM.
I MEAN, HOW MANY TIMES
HAVE WE BEEN HERE?
THE KUNIE TRIBE IS TRICKY.
[NAOTSUGU]
THEY'D HAVE TO BE...
THOSE NPCS ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR
CIRCULATING ALL THE
WORLD'S CURRENCY
[HENRIETTA]
IT ISN'T JUST BANKING.
THEY ALSO MAINTAIN AND
DEPLOY THE ROYAL GUARD,
ALONG WITH THE MAGICAL PATHWAYS
THAT RESPAWN MONSTERS
AND ADVENTURERS.
AND THEIR MAGIC BARRIERS KEEP
MONSTERS OUT OF THE CITIES.
[SHIROE] SO WE CAN'T COME
TO AN ARRANGEMENT?
TO DO SO WOULD BREAK LAWS
DATING BACK TO MY ANCESTORS
HMM...
[EINS] WELL THEN, DO YOU THINK
WE COULD TALK THE KUNIE
INTO GIVING US A LOAN?
[SHIROE]
NO, I WOULDN'T BET ON IT
THE GUILD BUILDING, WHICH
INCLUDES ALL LOCAL BANKING,
THE CATHEDRAL AND
THE TRADE CENTER
ARE AMONG THE RESOURCES
WE PURCHASED.
WE DID THAT IN ORDER TO PLACE
THEM
UNDER CONTROL OF THE
ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE.
WE WANTED TO BE SURE THAT
NO ONE ELSE
WAS ABLE TO USE THEM
AS THEIR OWN.
HOWEVER...
"HOWEVER", THE MAINTENANCE
COSTS ARE NUTS!
ALL THOSE BUILDINGS ARE
TAKING TEN MILLION IN GOLD
OUT OF OUR ACCOUNTS
EVERY MONTH!
NOW WAIT... I REMEMBER THE
PURCHASE OF THE GUILD BUILDING
AND IT WAS ONLY FIVE MILLION
IN GOLD AT THE TIME.
AND WE'RE PAYING
ALMOST DOUBLE THAT
TO HANG ON TO THEM
EVERY MONTH?
YEAH, AND THE ROUND TABLE
CONFERENCE IS GONNA WIND UP
GOING BANKRUPT BEFORE
TOO LONG...
[SOJIRO] WE'RE NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO HOLD
OUR PARTIES OR
FESTIVALS ANYMORE.
[EINS] I REALLY DON'T THINK
THAT'S THE ISSUE AT HAND HERE?
[WOODSTOCK]
HAS THIS THING GONE PUBLIC YET?
[SHIROE] NO.
IT WOULDN'T BE WISE TO MAKE
THIS INFORMATION PUBLIC,
NOT WITH UNWELCOME
EARS OUT THERE.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
MINAMI, AREN'T YOU?
YES, WE BELIEVE FROM
PLANT HWYADEN...
THE PEOPLE ON THE STREET ARE
ALREADY TALKING ABOUT THEM.
I HEARD EVERYONE IN MINAMI BOWS
TO PLANT HWYADEN
LIKE IT'S SOME KIND
OF DICTATORSHIP.
YES, BUT THEY'RE DOING
OKAY, AREN'T THEY?
I'VE GOT A FRIEND OVER THERE
WHO TOLD ME ALL ABOUT IT...
POLITICALLY THINGS
ARE KINDA SCREWED.
[SHIROE] NOT ALL DICTATORS
HURT THEIR PEOPLE, BUT...
[SOJIRO] YOU KNOW,
I SURE DO WISH KRUSTY AND
ISAAC'S GUILDS WERE BACK.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] FATE DEALT
US A PRETTY BIG BLOW
WHEN THE GAME SERVER KICKED OFF
THE "RETURN OF THE
GOBLIN KING" EVENT
AND THE GOBLIN ARMY STARTED
STAMPEDING ALL OVER EVERYTHING.
AFTER THEIR VICTORY
IN THE RAID AT ZANTLEAF,
THE AKIHABARA ADVENTURERS BEGAN
TO INVADE THE GOBLIN ARMY'S
STRONGHOLD IN SEVENTH FALL.
KRUSTY AND ISAAC SERVE AS
OUR GENERALS OUT THERE.
KARASHIN AND AKANEYA
ARE ALSO THERE
FOR TECHNICAL AND
LOGISTICAL SUPPORT.
BUT THE BATTLE GUILDS
HAVE IT COVERED
I DON'T THINK MINAMI'S GOING
TO POSE MUCH OF A THREAT
TO US IN THE NEAR FUTURE.
FINE, SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
(EXHALE)
(EXCITED CHATTERING)
[SERARA]
HEY! THANKS FOR WAITING!
I THINK YOU'LL FIND
A LITTLE HINT OF PUMPKIN
IN MANY OF THE ITEMS
ON THE MENU TONIGHT.
(GROANING)
YEAH, IT'S TASTY
I'M GETTING THE FEELING
HE PUT PUMPKIN IN EVERYTHING
CHIEF NYANTA, DO YOU HAVE
ANYTHING WITHOUT PUMPKIN IN IT?
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY
NUTRIENTS ARE IN A PUMPKIN?
NOT TO MENTION THIS PUPPY
CAN KEEP YOU WARM AT NIGHT.
YOU'RE PARTICIPATING IN
A PUMPKIN FEAST,
DON'T DISRESPECT, LITTLE MAN.
I'M SORRY, CHIEF...
URR... WAHHH... I WANT MEAT!
[ISUZU]
WELL D. D. D. CAME IN FIRST.
AND THE BLACK SWORD
KNIGHTS TOOK SECOND.
[MINORI] TENTH PLACE IS ACTUALLY
STILL PRETTY GOOD FOR US.
YEAH... SO WHAT'S THAT THING
YOU GOT THERE, MINORI?
(STRANGE MOOING)
SOME WEIRD OLD GUY
JUST WALKED UP TO ME AND SAID IT
WAS OUR PRIZE FOR TENTH PLACE.
WELL IT'S KINDA FREAKY!
[TOYA] FU‐WOAH! THAT'S A
STUFFED FUZZY GOAT SLIME!
[RUDY] REALLY!? IS THIS ONE OF
THOSE DISGUSTINGLY CUTE ITEMS
I'VE BEEN HEARING
EVERYONE TALK ABOUT?
BOYS ARE SO CRAZY ABOUT THINGS
THAT ARE ALL GRODY, AREN'T THEY?
WHEN IT COMES TO
IMMATURE STUFF LIKE THAT,
YOU'RE SUCH AN ADULT,
MISTER CAT!
[MARIELLE] WELL THAT'S
DISAPPOINTING TO HEAR...
[SERARA, UNDER] YOU'RE SO
GROWN UP AND REFINED
[HENRIETTA] OKAY, I'M HERE,
WHERE IS SHIROE?
UH MINORI...
IS IT JUST ME OR...
DID BIG BROTHER SHIROE
PULL A NO‐SHOW
FOR ANOTHER ONE
OF OUR PARTIES?
HMMM... APPARENTLY HE'S
CATCHING UP ON HIS WORK AGAIN.
HMMM...
WHY DO I GET THE FEELING
HIS BAD HABIT IS CATCHING UP
WITH HIM AGAIN?
I DON'T LIKE IT...
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THE
ONLY WAY TO GET IT DONE.
WHEWW!
(LAUGHING)
HEY! WE SHOULD PRESENT THIS
GLORIOUSLY SLIMY TROPHY
TO MASTER SHIROE!
UH, TOTALLY!
THAT'S AN AWFUL IDEA.
(LAUGH)
HEY SHIROE!
GOOD WORK OUT THERE!
HEY, THANKS.
MY LORD! MY LORD!
(STRANGE MOO)
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS...
WE GOT IT FOR TENTH PLACE
UH... Y‐YEAH? THAT'S GREAT!
MASTER SHIROE!
I'M GLAD YOU MADE IT OUT!
UH? OH UH, THANK YOU MINORI.
SO UH, I GUESS
WORK'S BEEN DIFFICULT
(DISAPPOINTED MOO)
YEAH, KIND OF...
[SHIROE] SO THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL ALL OF YOU.
OH YEAH?
OKAY...
WHAT KINDA NEWS IS IT?
RIGHT...
IT'S LIKE THIS...
I'M PROBABLY GONNA HAVE TO
LEAVE THE CITY FOR A WHILE.
(GASPS)
NO YOU CAN'T...!
THAT'S NOT HAPPENING!
DON'T FORGET THAT
CHRISTMAS IS COMING UP!
THERE! HA! I GOT YOU!
YOU CAN'T LEAVE BEFORE
CHRISTMAS, MISTER STRATEGIST!
THAT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
HMMM...
(DOOR OPENING)
WELCOME BACK.
HOW'D IT LOOK?
IT'S FINE OUT THERE.
A LITTLE SNOW... AND A LITTLE
BIT OF A BREEZE.
[SHIROE]
THAT'S GOOD. THANKS.
[NAOTSUGU]
SURE THING!
HERE YOU GO...
OH...?
MMM.
SO... YOU GONNA TELL
ME WHAT'S GOING ON
OR ARE YOU GONNA
JUST KEEP GRUNTING?
HMM?
IT'S BEEN TEN DAYS
SINCE YOU BROUGHT IT UP.
[MINORI]
YOU'RE LEAVING AKIHABARA?
PLEASE TALK TO US, WHAT BROUGHT
THIS ON ALL OF A SUDDEN?
[SHIROE]
I KNOW I'VE BEEN
A LITTLE SECRETIVE
ABOUT THIS WITH EVERYONE...
BUT HERE'S THE THING,
YOU GUYS...
THE CITY IS IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
(GASPS)
[SHIROE]
I CAN'T GO INTO DETAILS...
BUT I HAVE TO DO THIS BECAUSE
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO HANDLE IT.
OF COURSE, MY LORD...
COULD YOU...
TELL US WHERE YOU'RE
GOING AT LEAST?
[SHIROE]
I REALLY CAN'T, ISUZU...
I DON'T LIKE IT...
I WISH OUR GUILD MASTER
COULD TRUST US MORE...
BUT IT'S FINE.
[MINORI, THINKING]
HE HAS A GOOD REASON.
THERE MIGHT BE A SPY FROM MINAMI
IN THE CITY SOMEWHERE.
[MINORI]
A LEAK FROM ANY ONE OF US,
NO MATTER HOW "SMALL"
OR "HARMLESS"
COULD CAUSE A PROBLEM.
[SHIROE]
THAT'S RIGHT.
[RUDY]
WELL THAT MAKES SENSE I GUESS.
THAT'S ONE WAY TO KEEP
US QUIET ANYWAY.
HAVE YOU TOLD ANYONE ON
THE ROUND TABLE ABOUT THIS?
[SHIROE]
KRUSTY NEEDS TO KNOW,
ALONG WITH SOJIRO AND ISAAC.
COMBAT GUILD LEADERS.
IF ANYONE CAN DO THIS,
GUILD LEADER SHIROE‐ECHHI WILL
FIND A WAY TO MAKE IT WORK!
(ALL AGREEING)
THANKS A LOT, CHIEF.
AND NOW THAT WE'VE GOTTEN
THAT STRAIGHTENED OUT.
NAOTSUGU, I NEED‐
NO, YOU DON'T...
HUH?
PITCHERS NEED
THEIR CATCHERS, BUD.
AND AN ENCHANTER
NEEDS HIS GUARDIAN.
NO WAY I'M STAYING HERE,
YOU GOT THAT?
(EXHALE)
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD!
HUH?
I‐I'M GOING, TOO!
AKATSUKI, I NEED YOU
TO STAY BEHIND IN THE CITY.
OH?
(INHALES)
I'VE GOT A SPECIAL TASK
THAT ONLY YOU ARE
CAPABLE OF COMPLETING.
SO, WHY DID WE COME
ALL THE WAY UP HERE
IN THE SNOW LOOKIN' FOR CASH?
FOR ONE THING, YOU CAN'T GET
WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR
BY SLAYING MONSTERS
OR COMPLETING THE KNOWN QUESTS.
THAT WOULD TAKE TOO LONG.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
THE GRAND TOTAL...
SITS SOMEWHERE AROUND
EIGHTY TRILLION.
(TOCCATA AND FUGUE PLAYS)
WOOOOOAAAAHHHH!
E‐EIGHTY TRILLION?!
RIGHT.
I DID THE MATH
AND FIGURED OUT
HOW MUCH EVERY ADVENTURER
IN THE WORLD HAD
AND EVEN THEN WE'D FALL
WELL SHORT OF OUR GOAL.
WAIT, WOULD WE NEED ALL OF THAT
JUST TO KEEP CONTROL
OF EVERYTHING
WE ALREADY HAVE?
HMMM?
[REGAN]
EXCUSE ME...
HMM?
UM, MASTER SHIROE.
PARDON ME, BUT IT WOULD APPEAR
YOUR GUEST HAS ARRIVED
THEN WHAT'RE YOU LURKIN'
AROUND LIKE A CREEP FOR?
IT'S BEEN QUITE A
WHILE HASN'T IT?
THAT ALL DEPENDS ON
YOUR PERSPECTIVE.
LET ME INTRODUCE
YOU TO REGAN.
HOWEVER, YOU MAY KNOW HIM BETTER
AS THE MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE.
[NAOTSUGU, THINKING]
I'VE SEEN HIS NAME
IN FLAVOR TEXT LIKE
A ZILLION TIMES,
BUT THERE WASN'T
ANYTHING IN THERE
SAYING HOW SKETCHY
LOOKIN' HE WAS.
I SEE IT, BUT I STILL
DON'T BELIEVE IT.
[KINJO]
YES, OF COURSE.
I SERVE AS THE LIAISON
OFFICER FOR THE KUNIE TRIBE.
MY NAME IS KINJO.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
OH, IT IS A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU, TOO!
WHAT AN HONOR TO MEET A
MEMBER OF THE KUNIE TRIBE.
SUCH A TREAT.
LIKEWISE.
I FIND MYSELF BEFORE
THE MASTER STRATEGIST
WHO REPRESENTS ADVENTURERS.
AS WELL AS THE ONE AND ONLY
MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE, REGAN.
[KINJO]
I DOUBT EVEN MY GREAT ANCESTORS
COULD HAVE PREDICTED SUCH
AN IMPRESSIVE GATHERING.
(EXHALES)
IT TRULY IS WONDERFUL
TO HAVE YOU JOINING US.
THE FACE THAT YOU'VE
AGREED TO THIS MEETING
MAKES THE GRAVITY OF THIS
GATHERING QUIET ASTONISHING.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
WHEN I THINK OF THE
POWER OF THE KUNIE TRIBE
AND THE ARTS AND SPELLS OF
THE MAGIC USER'S CIVILIZATION,
MY HEART JUST SWELLS
WITH ANTICIPATION!
ANTICIPATION?
OH YES! EVEN MASTER
SHIROE CAN'T HELP
BUT BE JUST GIDDY
THINKING ABOUT IT!
REALLY? DON'T YOU THINK
THAT'S A BIT MUCH?
(EXHALES)
[SHIROE]
LET'S GET BACK TO THE REASON
I ASKED YOU HERE, ALL RIGHT?
[KINJO] I REMEMBER YOU SAID
SOMETHING ABOUT FUNDING.
DID YOU NEED A LOAN FROM US?
[SHIROE] YES. WE TALKED ABOUT
THIS BRIEFLY IN THE CITY.
[KINJO]
BUT YOU STILL WANTED TO COME
ALL THE WAY UP HERE
TO NEGOTIATE.
I'M GUESSING THAT WAS TO PROVE
YOU KNEW OUR WHEREABOUTS?
REGAN HAD A LITTLE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THAT.
[KINJO]
OH, REALLY
AND I SUPPOSE THAT'S IN
THE RECORDS AT MIRROR LAKE?
[SHIROE] NOT PRECISELY,
BUT WITH HIS HELP,
I WAS ABLE TO DEDUCE THAT
THE KUNIE TRIBE'S VILLAGE
IS NEAR THE
TEAR STONE MOUNTAINS.
I SUPPOSE IT'S MY WAY OF SAYING,
"HEY, I KNOW WHERE YOU LIVE."
HONESTLY, AS THREATS GO,
IT'S PRETTY CLICHE.
[KINJO] ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
I'D LOVE TO HELP YOU,
BUT I'M AFRAID A LOAN
SIMPLY IS NOT POSSIBLE.
YOU ALREADY KNOW.
ALREADY KNOW WHAT?
THAT IT WOULD VIOLATE EDICTS
LAID DOWN BY MY ANCESTORS.
(EXHALE) HMM...
[SHIROE, THINKING] IT WOULD SEEM
MY RESEARCH WAS DEAD ON.
REGARDLESS OF WHETHER ITS
FOR A LOAN OR AN INVESTMENT,
THE BANKS HERE DON'T CONTRIBUTE
TO INCREASING THE MONEY SUPPLY.
BANK ARE JUST THAT, BANKS.
PLACES TO PUT YOUR MONEY AND
GET IT BACK WHEN YOU WANT IT.
MONEY LENDING,
EVEN FOR A FAIR INTEREST RATE,
ISN'T A PRACTICE IN THIS WORLD.
(ROAR)
[SHIROE, THINKING] SO BASICALLY,
IF YOU WANT GOLD...
YOU HAVE TO BE IN THE BUSINESS
OF DESTROYING MONSTERS.
AND THAT MEANS THERE'S ONE JOB
AND ONE WAY TO GET PAID FOR IT.
NO OTHER CURRENCIES.
OKAY SO LET ME ASK
YOU SOMETHING, KINJO.
IS THE ONLY WAY TO EARN
GOLD TO DEFEAT MONSTERS?
YES, THAT'S CORRECT.
AND OCCASIONALLY WE CAN
GO ON A DUNGEON QUESTION,
[SHIROE] AND WE CAN GET HUNDREDS
OF GOLD PIECES THAT WAY?
[KINJO]
OF COURSE. YOU ARE, AFTER ALL,
SHOWING A GREAT AMOUNT
OF BRAVERY.
[SHIROE] IF THE KUNIE TRIBE
IS UNWILLING TO GIVE US A LOAN,
[SHIROE]
I MUST CONSIDER ANOTHER OPTION.
I MIGHT JUST HAVE TO
TAKE THAT GOLD
FROM ITS CENTRAL
DISTRIBUTION POINT.
I IMAGINE THAT WOULD CAUSE YOU
A GREAT DEAL OF TROUBLE.
I'M SURE YOU'D
WANT TO AVOID THAT.
EH? HMM...
UH? HUH?
WAIT A MINUTE, SHIROE!
YOU SAYING WHAT I THINK
YOU'RE SAYING?
[NAOTSUGU, THINKING] OKAY, SO
THAT'S HOW THE GAME WORKS:
WE BEAT A MONSTER, GOLD POPS UP.
PRACTICALLY OUT OF NOWHERE.
IT JUST SHOOTS UP. INSTANTLY.
I MEAN IT MAKES SENSE
IN A GAME.
HACK, SLASH, GET GOLD.
MONSTERS RESPAWN.
HACK, SLASH, GET MORE GOLD.
AND SO BASICALLY, SHIROE THINKS
THERE MUST BE A SOURCE
OF ALL THE COINS THAT APPEAR
WHEN MONSTERS COME BACK TO LIFE.
THAT'S A HELL OF A RISK, BUDDY,
'CAUSE YOU'RE PROBABLY
THE ONLY ONE OUT THERE
WHO THINKS SOMETHING
LIKE THAT EVEN EXISTS.
AND YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S THE WAY IT WORKS?
THE SPIRITUAL THEORY EXPLAINS
HOW THE MONSTERS
COME BACK TO LIFE.
BUT WHY ARE THEY REINCARNATED
WITH THE SAME AMOUNT OF RICHES?!
WELL OF COURSE!
IT WOULD ONLY MAKE SENSE THAT
THERE'D BE A MECHANISM IN PLACE!
NOT ONLY DID MY STUDIES FIND
THAT THERE WAS A MECHANISM,
BUT SOMEONE BEHIND IT
TO MAKE IT POSSIBLE!
AND VOILA!
I FOUND THE KUNIE!
A TRIBE IN CHARGE
OF ALL THE GOLD.
[REGAN] IN THE LOWEST LAYER
OF THE DEPTHS OF PALM,
MY TEXT SAID THERE IS A
GIGANTIC WHIRLPOOL OF GOLD
THAT DAZZLES THE EYE!
AND IT WAS SEALED AWAY
BY A MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE
FIFTEEN GENERATIONS AGO.
HAH. OH MY...
[SHIROE] I'VE ALREADY VERIFIED
THAT IT'S THERE.
THERE'S AN AREA THAT'S
BEEN SEALED OFF
WITH MAGIC FROM MIRROR LAKE.
CRACKING IT OPEN
SHOULDN'T BE THAT HARD.
NOW YOU TELL ME WHAT
YOU WERE OUT THERE FOR.
[KINJO] INTERESTING. SO YOU
SPENT YOUR TIME RESEARCHING US,
SO YOU CAN ACQUIRE
A WHIRLPOOL OF GOLD.
YES.
AND YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY POSITIVE
ALL THIS GOLD BELONGS
TO MY TRIBE.
I AM.
WELL THEN, WHEN YOU SAY
YOU WANT TO "TAKE" THE GOLD
FROM ITS SOURCE...
DOESN'T THAT MEAN YOU'RE
INTENDING TO "STEAL" IT FROM US?
ARE YOU SAYING
THE ROUND TABLE
HAS DESIGNS ON
PILLAGING OUR GOLD?
THAT'S ACTUALLY THE
REASON I CALLED YOU
WE DO NO WANT TO STAND
ON ANTAGONISTIC TERMS
WITH THE KUNIE TRIBE.
I KNOW WHAT MY TRIBE
DOES WITH IT,
WHAT WOULD YOU DO WITH IT?
HM?
IF I WERE TO TELL YOU,
WOULD IT CHANGE IN ANY WAY
WHETHER OR NOT YOU WILL HELP US?
(EXHALES)
(LOG BREAKING, FIRE CRACKLING)
[KINJO]
I'M AFRAID NOT...
THERE'S STILL THE MATTER
OF THE ANCIENT LAW.
(NAOTSUGU AND SHIROE EXHALE)
[REGAN]
SO WHY DID MASTER SHIROE
BOTHER DISCUSSING THIS
WITH MASTER KINJO AT ALL?
IT OCCURS TO ME THAT YOU
COULD'VE GONE DOWN THERE
AND STARTED STEALING
THE GOLD, ALREADY.
[NAOTSUGU] IT MIGHT BE TRUE
THAT, FROM TIME TO TIME,
SHIROE IS THE
"VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES".
BUT NOT WHEN HE HAS A CHANCE
TO MAKE A FRIEND INSTEAD.
HUH? MAKE A FRIEND?
[NAOTSUGU]
HONESTY'S IMPORTANT TO HIM.
AND TIPTOEING AROUND THE TRUTH
LIKE THAT WOULD'VE BEEN A LIE.
HE'S ALMOST TOO HONEST
FOR HIS OWN GOOD.
[REGAN]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ALL I HAD TO DO WAS SIT THERE,
AND WATCH BOTH OF 'EM
TALK TO EACH OTHER...
THEY BOTH KEEP SECRETS.
WHEN YOU MAKE A NEW BUSINESS
CONTACT WITH SOMEONE,
YOU GOTTA DROP
SOME OF THAT CRAP,
LEARN ABOUT WHAT MAKES
THE OTHER GUY TICK,
AND THEN BE UP FRONT ABOUT
WHAT YOUR SIDE IN THE
NEGOTIATION WANTS...
FINALLY, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO MAKE COMPROMISES,
AND WHEN YOU'RE ON THE LEVEL,
YOU USUALLY GET WHAT YOU WANT.
[REGAN]
OHHH...
DID YOU HAPPEN TO BE A
MERCHANT, MASTER NAOTSUGU?
LET'S JUST SAY I CAN
TAKE CARE OF BUSINESS.
"BIZ‐NESS..."
I'M BETTING THAT
JUST HAPPENS TO BE
A NEGOTIATION TALENT.
OKAY... LOOKS LIKE I NEED
TO GO TALK TO HIM AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT... SO WHAT DO YOU
THINK HE MEANT BY THAT?
HM?
[KINJO]
IT'S SETTLED...
WE'LL MEET AT
THE MEANDERING RIVER
AND FORGOTTEN
UNDERGROUND GARDEN...
THIS IS THE POINT AT WHICH
THE GOLD COINS THAT APPEAR
FROM THE VOID,
RETURN TO THE VOID.
[BOTH]
HUH?
I'D SUGGEST BRINGING
SOME FRIENDS...
YOU'RE GOING TO BE
NEEDING THEM, I'M SURE.
IT WON'T BE EASY GETTING DOWN
TO THE BOTTOM OF THE FOUNTAIN.
WE'LL MONITOR YOUR
GROUP'S PERFORMANCE...
IF YOUR RESPONSE TO THE
CHALLENGE IS SATISFACTORY,
WE WILL CONSIDER YOUR REQUEST.
[SHIROE]
"BRING A FEW FRIENDS..."
I THINK WE ALL KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
IT'LL BE A HUGE BATTLE.
WE'LL NEED A FULL RAID PARTY.
WHOA...
[SHIROE] THE DEPTHS OF PALM
HAS A RAID ZONE AT THE BOTTOM.
IF WE DON'T CLEAR IT,
WE DON'T GET THE GOLD.
I'M NOT EXPECTING IT TO BE EASY.
[NAOTSUGU]
WE'RE DEFINITELY GONNA NEED
A RAID PARTY FOR THAT.
[SHIROE] YEAH, BUT THERE'S
NO WAY WE CAN CALL
SOMEONE FROM THE ROUND TABLE
TO JOIN US.
WE CAN'T TAKE THE CHANCE
OF MINAMI FINDING OUT.
THEY COULD ONLY SEE IT AS
AN OPPORTUNITY TO MAKE A MOVE.
OKAY SO WHO DO
WE CALL FOR HELP?
I THINK I HAVE SOMEONE IN MIND.
CAREFUL MY LORD...
[SHIROE]
I BLEW IT...
I DIDN'T ACCOUNT FOR
ALL THE VARIABLES
AND I DIDN'T TRUST EVERYONE
TO GET THEIR PARTS DONE.
[SHIROE]
AKATSUKI? DID YOU... DIE?
MM‐HMM.
YEAH, WELL...
I DIDN'T MAKE IT EITHER.
SO THIS IS WHAT IT'S LIKE...
[AKATSUKI]
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
IT WAS A PRETTY CRAZY
CHRISTMAS EVE, MY LORD.
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
THEY HAVE DESCENDED UPON
THE NORTHERN LAND.
AND THERE, THEY FIND A MAN.
WILLIAM MASSACHUSETTS.
GUILD MASTER OF
A PROUD RAID‐GUILD,
THIS MAN TOLD SHIROE
HE WASN'T INTERESTED
IN PROTECTING AKIHABARA BUT,
THERE IS ONE OTHER MAN.
HIS NAME IS DEMICAS.
SHIROE TOOK HIS LIFE ONCE.
[SHIROE]
STAND UP... ONE MORE TIME!