[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] SO THIS IS
ULLR OF THE NINTH GARDEN...
THE ABYSSAL SHAFT'S
FINAL RAID BOSS.
EVEN IF I HAD ALL OF SILVER
SWORD WITH ME RIGHT NOW,
WE WOULDN'T STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST HIM... NOT EVEN CLOSE.
HE'S NOT JUST ANOTHER KINJO...
THE ONLY DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN THEM IS
THE COLOR OF THEIR BREASTPLATES.
OTHER THAN THAT... THEY'RE
PERFECT COPIES OF EACH OTHER.
MUST BE SOME SORT OF
KUNIE TRIBE THING
HUH?
OF COURSE... HE HAS TO
BE GETTING WORRIED.
I MEAN, WE KEEP COMING
BACK EVERY TIME WE DIE.
IT'S LIKE HE'S FACING
A PACK OF ZOMBIES.
WE NEVER STOP COMING...
THE ONLY THING KEEPING HIM HERE
AND FACING US
IS PRIDE AT THIS POINT.
THE PRIDE OF THE WHOLE OF YAMATO
AND THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
(DEATH SCREAM)
[ALL] WHOA!
(OOHS AND AHHS)
AAAW YEAH!
WAY TO GO GUYS! WOOHOO!
WE'VE ONLY GOT ONE MORE
LEFT! TAKE HIM DOWN!
(SCREAMING)
[DEMICAS]
(WHIMPERING) NO!
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
I'VE COME HERE TO SPEAK WITH
KINJO OF THE KUNIE TRIBE.
[KINJO] SINCE YOU HAVE
PERSEVERED AND SUCCESSFULLY
REACHED OUR INNER SANCTUM,
YOU MAY NOW HAVE YOUR AUDIENCE.
NOW THAT I'VE MADE IT ALL THE
WAY HERE,
I'M ASSUMING THIS IS WHERE
ALL THE GOLD COINS RECYCLE?
THAT IS CORRECT. AND
WE HAD AN AGREEMENT,
SO I'LL SHARE EVERYTHING YOU
WANT TO KNOW ABOUT THIS PLACE.
THIS IS WHERE ALL THE GOLD
IN YAMATO WAS CREATED.
AND IT ALL RETURNS
HERE ONCE IT'S SPENT.
THE KUNIE ARE HERE TO GUARD THIS
PROCESS, BUT IT IS SO INCREDIBLY
ANCIENT EVEN WE DO NOT FULLY
UNDERSTAND HOW IT WORKS.
THE GOLD FLOWS IN A GREAT
GLIMMERING RIVER,
RE‐SPAWNING MONSTERS.
IT'S PRACTICALLY ENDLESS.
THE ENGINE OF THIS IS BURIED
DEEP UNDERNEATH YAMATO'S LAND.
WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN COMMITTED TO
PROTECTING THE GOLD RESERVE,
AND NO ONE'S EVER
MADE IT THIS FAR...
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
THIS SYSTEM DISTRIBUTES
THE GOLD TO MONSTERS.
BACK IN OUR GAMING DAYS,
THE GOLD WAS JUST PART OF
THE PROGRAMMING. DIDN'T
REALLY THINK ABOUT IT.
THERE WASN'T ANY MALICE
OR MISINFORMATION.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] BUT NOW THAT
NPC PEOPLE OF THE LAND
ARE AWARE OF OUR SITUATION,
THEY MIGHT START WONDERING
WHY THE KUNIE RESURRECT
MONSTERS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
AND SINCE THE KUNIE ARE NPCS,
THAT MIGHT PUT THEM ON THE WRONG
SIDE OF A VERY LONG,
ONGOING CONFLICT.
IF I WERE IN THEIR TRIBE,
I'D BE A LITTLE WARY, TOO.
THEIR PERSPECTIVE
MUST BE CONSIDERED.
HERE'S THE DEAL,
WE WOULD LIKE TO
KEEP YOUR SECRET.
IT CAN BE SAFE WITH US.
IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS
THE KUNIE TRIBE HAVE UPHELD,
YOU ARE ENTITLED TO
TAKE THE GOLD...
HOWEVER THERE COULD BE
A PROBLEM I'M AFRAID.
IT CENTERS AROUND
THE INTERPRETATION
OF OUR ANCIENT EDICTS.
MUCH OF THE TEXT HAS BEEN LOST
OVER THE COURSE OF HISTORY.
TO PUT IT BLUNTLY, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TAKE
A THOUSAND COINS OR A
HUNDRED MILLION OF THEM.
I ALSO HAVE ANOTHER DUTY... AND
IT INVOLVES PASSING ON THE WORDS
OF MY ANCESTORS AS
A WARNING TO YOU.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
IT REALLY IS A LOT OF GOLD.
BUT EVEN SO,
JUST TO THINK OF ALL THE
PEOPLE I COULD HELP WITH THIS.
I WANT TO GIVE SOMETHING
BACK TO EVERYONE.
"BE WARY OF THE MISFORTUNE
THAT COMES WITH FORTUNE.
THESE GREAT RICHES
ARE NOT RICHES.
TAKE THESE WORDS TO HEART,
OR THY INNER BEAST WILL
CONSUME OUR WORLD."
THUS, IT WAS WRITTEN.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
BACK IN THE MOUNTAINS,
I COULDN'T TELL KINJO
WHAT I WAS AFTER.
BUT TODAY, I'M GOING
TO DO EXACTLY THAT!
(ROAR)
[SHIROE] UH?
(SHIROE EXHALES)
MM?
[KINJO]
WHAT WAS THAT...?
[SHIROE] OKAY, I HAVE BOUND AND
FINALIZED YOUR CONTRACT WITH US.
THE ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE
DOES NOT WANT YOUR GOLD.
AND WE DON'T NEED THE
GUILD BUILDING TITLE
IT'S OBSOLETE NOW.
IT HAS SERVED IT'S PURPOSE...
WE USED THE SYSTEM
TO PROTECT US UNTIL
WE ULTIMATELY LEARNED
TO DO IT OURSELVES
WE'RE GRATEFUL FOR THE HELP YOU
OFFERED US
IN PROTECTING AKIHABARA,
BUT WE'RE JUST IN
A BETTER PLACE NOW.
IF SOMETHING OUTSIDE THE CITY
WERE TO THREATEN US...
WE CAN HANDLE IT.
WHAT YOU JUST WITNESSED WAS
A CONTRACT BINDING TECHNIQUE
AND ALL I NEEDED TO
DO TO EXECUTE IT...
WAS TEAR THE CONTRACT IN HALF,
WE'RE DONE.
THERE'S NOTHING
HIDDEN WITHIN IT.
WE WILL TRANSFER OUR
TITLES TO THE GUILD HALL,
CATHEDRAL AND THE OVERALL
CITY OF AKIHABARA,
INCLUDING COMMERCIAL BUILDINGS
TO THE YAMATO SERVER FORTH WITH.
PLUS THIS TERMINATING THE
CONTRACT WILL MAKE THOSE
TRANSACTIONS PERMANENT.
[KINJO] UH...
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
WE PURCHASED ALL OF AKIHABARA'S
PRIMARY INSTITUTIONS TO KEEP
ANYONE FROM ABUSING THEM.
HOWEVER, ALL OF THIS WAS
DRAINING THE ROUND TABLE'S
FINANCES. RUNNING
US DRY OF CAPITAL.
WHICH IS WHY WE APPROACHED
THEM FOR A LOAN.
WE EXPLORED OTHER POSSIBILITIES
AND DISCUSSED OTHER
WAYS TO GET IT DONE...
FINALLY, WE DECIDED ON
MOUNTING THIS EXPEDITION.
I SEE... SO ALL THAT GOLD FROM
AKIHABARA
WAS YOU PURCHASING
ALL THE BUILDINGS.
[SHIROE] CORRECT. I'M SURPRISED
TO KNOW THAT AS MANAGERS
OF ALL THE GOLD YOU
WEREN'T AWARE OF THAT.
THE CONDITIONS FOR THE
TRANSACTION HAVE BEEN MET,
SO THE FUNDS FOR THE PURCHASES
RETURN HERE IN EXCHANGE
FOR THE CONTRACT. THAT'S
HOW IT'S DRAWN UP.
[KINJO] AND YOU CAME
ALL THE WAY DOWN HERE
JUST TO EXPLAIN THAT
TO ME, PERSONALLY?
IN A WAY, YES.
THAT STILL LEAVES THE
QUESTION ABOUT THE LOAN.
I WAS JUST GETTING TO THAT.
IN ADDITION... WE'D
LIKE TO PURCHASE
ALL OF THIS SERVER'S
FIELD ZONES,
ALL OF IT FROM THE FOREST, TO
THE MOUNTAIN RANGES TO THE LAKES
AND ANY FLATLANDS THAT HAVE NOT
BEEN CLAIMED.
YOU WANT TO BUY ALL
THE FIELD ZONES?
[SHIROE] AND JUST LIKE THE
TRANSACTION
WE COMPLETED A MOMENT AGO,
WE WILL TRANSFER THOSE
TITLES TO THE SERVER.
OUR GOAL FOR THIS IS TO
ELIMINATE THE POSSIBILITY
OF ANYONE ELSE
PURCHASING A ZONE.
[KINJO] IF I
UNDERSTAND CORRECTLY,
YOU'RE DOING THIS TO KEEP YOUR
ENEMIES FROM OWNING THEM.
THERE IS MORE TO IT THAN THAT.
AS IT STANDS PEOPLE OF THE
LAND CAN'T PURCHASE A ZONE,
ONLY ADVENTURERS.
[KINJO]
OH...
[SHIROE] THAT SEEMS A
LITTLE UNFAIR TO ME,
CREATING AN IMBALANCE
OF CITIZENSHIP
COULD ONLY LEAD TO PROBLEMS.
[KINJO]
HMMM...
NOW IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE AGAINST
THE IDEA OF OWNING PROPERTY.
HOWEVER, WE WOULD NEED TO DRAW
UP ANOTHER CONTRACT OF COURSE.
SO I WILL ASK YOU ONE MORE
TIME TO GIVE US A LOAN...
PLEASE HELP US AVOID BRINGING
ABOUT OUR OWN DESTRUCTION.
A LOAN INSURES ALL FUNDS WILL
BE RETURNED TO THE SOURCE.
AND YAMATO'S LAND
WILL RETURN TO YAMATO.
(EXHALE)
[KINJO] WELL, MASTER SHIROE AS
IT STANDS, I AM IN YOUR DEBT.
(GRUNTS)
[WILLIAM]
(EXHALE) UH...? HMPH!
MPH.... HUH?
OH MY GOD...
(LAUGHTER)
[WILLIAM, THINKING]
I DON'T BELIEVE IT! WE DID IT!
(LAUGHING)
[WILLIAM, THINKING] MY GUILD...
MY FRIENDS... ARE AMAZING!
[WILLIAM, VOICEOVER] I MEAN,
THESE GUYS REALLY ARE
THE BEST OF THE BEST!
WE WON...?
YEAH, WE DID IT!
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
AMAZING...
[PROMETHEUS] MY GOD LOOK
AT ALL THAT YOU GUYS!
I'VE NEVER SEEN SO MUCH GOLD!
THAT'S LITERALLY A
MOUNTAIN OF EPIC ITEMS!
SO, NORMALLY WHEN WE BEAT A
RAID BOSS FOR THE FIRST TIME,
IT'S CUSTOMARY FOR THE GUILD
MASTER TO DIVVY EVERYTHING UP.
THE LUNAR FLOWER CHARM!
I'D LIKE TO GIVE THIS, TO
THE MAN WHO LED THE WAY!
[DEMICAS]
HMPH... HUH?
MPH... WHAT'S THAT?
[ELTON DISKA] I CAN FEEL
A CHANGE IN THE AIR.
IT'S GETTING ALL WARM
AND SNUGLY IN HERE.
WHAT THE HELL DID YOU
DO IN THERE SHIROE?
[WILLIAM] LISTEN UP! THIS
IS A GREAT ITEM, GUYS!
IT'S FULL OF RESISTANCE BOOSTS
AND A LOT OF GREAT ABILITIES.
I THINK IT'S FITTING FOR
THE VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES!
I KNOW HE'S NOT IN OUR
GUILD OR ANYTHING,
BUT HE FOUGHT BY OUR SIDE
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE HERE!
WHAT DO YOU SAY, MAN?
YEAH!
HYUH!
(GIGGLES)
(AGREEING)
(LAUGHING)
[BOTH]
HM...?
OH...?
UH...
ALL OUR NAMES HAVE BEEN
ENGRAVED ON THIS MONOLITH!
SILVER SWORD AND
OUR PARTNERS ARE
THE FIRST ADVENTURERS
TO CONQUER THIS RAID!
(CHEERING)
(PING)
[SHIROE]
YEAH... UH‐HUH, RIGHT. I'M FINE.
IT'S OVER, AKATSUKI.
(STREET CHATTER)
[HENRIETTA]
MARIELLE!
ARE YOU FINISHED GETTING
READY YET...? MARIELLE?
(DOOR CREAKING)
OH‐UH?
UWAH!
WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THIS?!
(NERVOUS LAUGHTER)
WAHHH!
OH... MY GOODNESS.
[MARIELLE]
WHAT AM I TO DO?!
I CAN'T DECIDED WHAT I
WANNA WEAR OH‐OH‐OUUWWWW!
YOUR NORMAL ATTIRE SHOULD
BE PERFECTLY FINE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM IN OVER A
MONTH!
I WANNA LOOK EXTRA CUTE
WHEN HE SEES ME!
I WANNA BE DOLLED UP AND SUPER
SEXY AND TOTALLY BLOW HIS MIND!
I WANT HIM TO FREAK OUT AND NOT
KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH HIMSELF
[HENRIETTA] (SIGH) HAVE
IT YOUR WAY MARIELLE,
BUT I'M SURE HE'LL BE THRILLED
NO MATTER WHAT YOU'RE WEARING!
(LAUGH)
[RUDY] JUST LOOK... I'M
THE PICTURE OF ELEGANCE!
(BOTH SIGHING)
OKAY...
WHAT'RE YOU DOING WEARING
ALL THOSE FANCY CLOTHES?
IT'S TO MAKE AN IMPRESSION ON
OUR NEW RECRUIT...
AS A SENIOR GUILDMATE,
I COULDN'T BE
SEEN IN SUCH SHABBY RAGS.
[ISUZU] LOOKING LIKE A DANDY
FOP ISN'T GOING TO HELP YOU!
[MINORI] EXCUSE ME,
CHIEF NYANTA,
SHOULDN'T WE BE ON
OUR WAY TO MEET THEM?
IT'S STILL A LITTLE
EARLY FOR THAT.
(NERVOUS LAUGH) YEAH, I GUESS
YOU'RE RIGHT.
BUT YOU KNOW... THERE'S
ALWAYS THE POSSIBILITY
THEY'LL SHOW UP EARLY, RIGHT?
[AKATSUKI]
TAKE IT EASY, MINORI!
UH...?
IF I KNOW MY LORD... HE'LL BE
EXACTLY ON TIME AS ALWAYS.
[MINORI]
(EXHALE) MISS AKATSUKI...?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT
IT TOGETHER, GIRL!
(EXHALE)
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] AFTER
CLEARING THE RAID,
WE TOOK A LITTLE DETOUR
BACK TO SUSUKINO.
[NAOTSUGU] AH, COME ON, KNOCK IT
OFF! COME ON, STOP...!
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] I DISCUSSED
A GREAT DEAL OF THINGS
WITH SILVER SWORD ON
OUR WAY BACK...
HOWEVER, WE STILL HAVE
A LOT TO TALK ABOUT.
ESPECIALLY ABOUT WHAT'S HAPPENED
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE.
(GROWL, CHOMP)
[DEMICAS, VOICEOVER]
LISTEN, BOY...
YOU WILL CALL ME BY MY NAME.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER]
UP UNTIL THAT DAY,
I'D NEVER USED HIS
REAL NAME, HAD I?
NOT SURE WHY.
I SUPPOSE THE REAL REASON
I NEVER SAID IT...
WAS DUE TO THE FACT THAT
I WAS ANGRY WITH MYSELF.
I WAS ACCUSTOMED
TO BEING IN CONTROL,
AND I DEFINITELY
WASN'T AT THAT POINT.
AND HERE HE WAS, TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF PEOPLE,
AND I COULDN'T DO ANYTHING.
I GUESS IT WAS MY
WAY OF PRETENDING
THAT KIND OF PERSON
DIDN'T EXIST.
BUT IT WASN'T HAPPENING.
IT WAS IMMATURE OF ME.
I COULD'VE REASONED WITH HIM.
BUT I DIDN'T EVEN TRY...
DEMICAS, YOU CAN BE A REAL
JERK, YOU KNOW THAT?
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW... IT'S NOT
LIKE I REALLY LIKE YOU EITHER.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] WE MAY NEVER
BE FRIENDS. AND THAT'S OKAY.
WE AGREED TO TOLERATE
ONE ANOTHER.
AND SOMETIMES THAT'S THE
BEST YOU CAN HOPE FOR.
[REGAN] Y‐YOU WHAT?!
BOTH OF YOU DIED
DURING THE RAID?!
[NAOTSUGU] HEH...
[SHIROE] EHEHHEH...
[ALL] CHEERS! (LAUGHING)
HEY, UH... I THINK... I HEAR A
PARTY CALLING MY NAME, BRUH.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO GET HIM
TO SHUT UP SINCE YESTERDAY.
[TETORA] WANNA KNOW WHAT COLOR
MY PANTIES WERE WHEN I DIED?!
I BET YOU'RE DYING TO KNOW THAT!
NOT AT THE MOMENT...
HUH?!
TELL ME,
WHAT WAS IT LIKE TO
TRANSITION TO THE CATHEDRAL.
HOW WERE YOU REVIVED? AND AT THE
MOMENT OF YOUR DEATHS,
WHAT PRECISELY DID YOU SEE.
[TETORA] I'M OKAY NOW!
[REGAN] WHAT WAS THE
LAST THING YOU...EH?
[FEDERICO] THAT'S ENOUGH
[VOINEN] OKAY, OKAY.
LET'S GO FOR A LITTLE WALK.
(REGAN CRYING OUT)
[REGAN] HEY NOW! I'M JUST
FASCINATED
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
I WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING.
[REGAN] FILL ME IN!
I WANT THE WHOLE STORY!
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
[REGAN] I STILL HAVEN'T
FINISHED MY RESEARCH ON
THE TRANSPORT GATES
BETWEEN THE CITIES...
TILL THEN, I WILL
SEE YOU AGAIN SOON.
HAVE A SAFE JOURNEY, MY FRIEND.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] SILVER
SWORD ALSO REMAINED IN SUSUKINO.
THEY'LL REORGANIZE THEIR FORCES
AND PREPARE FOR FUTURE RAIDS
WHILE PROTECTING THEIR CITY.
[WILLIAM]
UH... HMM...
HUH?
JUST IN CASE...
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD AND
ADD ME TO YOUR FRIENDS LIST.
HMMM.
[SHIROE]
I ALREADY DID.
[WILLIAM]
OKAY, WELL THAT'S GOOD.
[DEMICAS]
BETTER BELIEVE IT!
I SAVED THAT DORK...
THAT BOY OWES ME BIG TIME!
[UPASHI]
OKAY, OKAY. GOOD FOR YOU.
HUH?! COME ON! I MEAN IT!
HE COULDN'T HAVE
DONE IT WITHOUT ME.
HE THANKED ME FOR IT
AND EVERYTHING!
HE WAS CRYING LIKE A BABY! AHH!
I HAD TO WIPE HIS NOSE... HUH?
HMMM...
UH... WHAT? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WELL, IT'S... IT'S JUST
THAT YOU'RE HAPPY.
HUH?!
MAKE ME HAPPY TOO...
[DEMICAS]
HMMM...
(GRIFFON CRIES)
[BOTH]
HUH?
OH COME ON... I WANTED TO
RIDE WITH YOU, NAOTSUGU!
MY GRIFFON HAS A HARD
ENOUGH TIME RIDING
WITH JUST ME AND
ALL THIS ARMOR!
WHATEVER! I BET YOU'RE SAVING
THAT SADDLE FOR SOMEBODY ELSE!
WHAT?! HEY! THAT IS NONE
OF YOUR BUSINESS, OKAY!
COULD YOU MAYBE TAKE
IT EASY ON THE GUY?
HUH? BUT I'M JUST HAVING A
LITTLE FUN WITH THE BIG LUG.
SO... YOU EVER GOING TO
TELL HIM YOU'RE A BOY...?
WHEN'S THE BIG REVEAL?
I'M JUST GONNA LET HIM STAY
NERVOUS AND CONFUSED UNTIL
HE FIGURES IT OUT. I MEAN IT'LL
BE A LOT MORE FUN THAT WAY!
(EXHALE) WELL I KINDA GET THE
FEELING YOU'RE WASTING
YOUR TIME... NAOTSUGU AND
MARIELLE ARE KIND OF A THING.
[TETORA] YEAH...
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, SHIROE!
WHY DID YOU LET THAT LITTLE
SPAZZY PANTS INTO OUR GUILD?
BECAUSE YOU NEEDED A STAR!
KAZUHIKO'S RECOMMENDATION
DIDN'T HURT.
HUH? WELL JUST SO YOU KNOW...
IT'S NOT LIKE I WENT TO SUSUKINO
UNDER ORDERS FROM KAZUHIKO
AND DID A BUNCH OF
SPY STUFF, OKAY?!
IT'S ALL RIGHT TETORA,
I BELIEVE YOU.
YOUR GUILD'S PRETTY STRONG,
YOU GUYS CAN HELP
OUT A LOT OF PEOPLE.
YEAH WELL, WE DIDN'T
START LOG HORIZON
TO BE SOME KIND OF A CHARITY.
YEAH, BUT... YOU STILL HAVE
FAITH IN THE WORLD...
AND YOU DON'T LET
EVERYONE'S INDIFFERENCE
KEEP YOU FROM HELPING PEOPLE.
MORE THAN THEY
DESERVE SOMETIMES.
HMPH?
[SHIROE, THINKING]
SHE'S SMARTER THAN I THOUGHT.
BETTER WATCH HER.
[ZELDEUS]
SO WHERE'S INTIX?
[MIZPHA] EASY, ZELDEUS...
SHE'LL BE HERE, SOON.
I TAKE IT THE PRINCESS
IS KEEPING HER?
I'M IN THE MOOD FOR A FIGHT...
NOT ENOUGH BLOOD THESE DAYS...
I DON'T WANT TO GET
OUT OF PRACTICE.
I'M TIRED OF JUST
SITTING AROUND WAITING.
BUT I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
IF IT'LL GET ME BACK
ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
[NAKARUNARD]
YOU'RE JUST POSTURING.
EVERYONE KNOWS YOU'RE HERE FOR
THE WINE
MORE THAN ANYTHING
ELSE, NPC. HMPH.
(YAWN)
[KUONG]
HOW LONG DO WE HAVE TO WAIT?
I JUST WANNA GET THIS OVER
WITH AND GET OUTTA HERE.
[JARED GUNN]
UP TOO LATE WERE WE?!
YOU SHOULDN'T STAY UP ALL NIGHT
STARING AT THE MOON, CHILD.
I'M JUST WAITING FOR
A GM TO CALL...
SO I CAN FINALLY
GET AWAY FROM YOU.
[LOREILE] ALL RIGHT THEN, IT
LOOKS LIKE THE PRINCESS
WON'T BE GRACING US
WITH HER PRESENCE.
HM?
[INTIX] TELL ME,
WHAT IS THE STATUS OF
AKIHABARA'S EXPEDITIONARY ARMY?
THEY'RE STILL IN THE SEVENTH
FALL AREA, FIGHTING GOBLINS.
VERY GOOD, AND THE ROYAL
GUARDSMAN IN AKIHABARA?
NUMBER ONE SAID HE WAS CAUGHT.
HE WAS RAISING QUITE
THE RUCKUS OVER THERE.
A ROYAL GUARDSMAN?
[KAZUHIKO]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
NO ONE TOLD ME
ABOUT ANY OF THIS.
WE DIDN'T WANT TO BOTHER
YOU... IT WAS A MINOR ISSUE.
HEH.
HMPH...
(EXHALE)
[KR] THE VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES
HAS MADE HIS WAY BACK TO TOWN.
(SURPRISED)
[KR] IT KIND OF MAKES ME WONDER
WHAT HE WAS DOING IN SUSUKINO.
OKAY, INTIX, WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
THAT RABBLE THAT REFUSES TO
MARCH TO THE BEAT
OF YOUR DRUM HAS RETURNED.
(GIGGLE)
[NAOTSUGU] YOU KNOW, I'M STILL
SURPRISED YOU DECIDED
TO JUST GIVE THE ZONES
BACK TO THE SERVER.
[SHIROE] I HAD NO IDEA IT WOULD
TURN INTO SUCH A BIG ORDEAL.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, WELL, SEEMS
LIKE EVERYTHING'S AN ISSUE.
EVER SINCE WE STARTED.
[SHIROE] HMPH... PRETTY
MUCH. KR USED TO HAVE
AN OLD SAYING FOR
TIMES LIKE THIS...
"BLAME YOUR BIRTH STARS AND
SIMPLY GIVE IN TO YOUR FATE."
(TETORA SQUEALS)
[BOTH] HUH?
[TETORA] SO, ARE THEY THE
OTHER MEMBERS OF LOG HORIZON?!
[SHIROE]
GUYS!
[NAOTSUGU] MARIELLE! (GRUNTS)
[TETORA](GIGGLE) HI, EVERYBODY!
YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY NICE OF
ALL OF YOU TO GET TOGETHER
TO MEET ME TODAY.
(NAOTSUGU STRUGGLES)
[RUDY] WELL NOW, SOMEBODY'S
SURE FULL OF THEMSELVES.
[ISUZU] AREN'T YOU ONE TO TALK?
[TOYA] THAT MUST BE TETORA...
DIDN'T KNOW SHE WAS A GIRL.
[MINORI] OH...
(LAUGHING)
[HENRIETTA] OH DEAR.
IT LOOKS AS IF THOSE
TWO ARE HOLDING HANDS.
[TETORA] GET READY TO
MEET YOUR NEW STARLET!
COME ON! I'M SERIOUS OKAY!
LEMME GO, YOU SKANK!
LET GO OF ME!
[TETORA] THANKS FOR WAITING!
(SHIROE EXHALES)
[TETORA] HEY EVERYBODY!
[NAOTSUGU] WHOA!
[ISUZU]
WELCOME BACK, MASTER SHIROE.
[RUDY] WE TOOK CARE OF
ALL THE IMPORTANT STUFF,
WHILE YOU WERE GONE.
[TOYA] WE WERE FIGHTING
GOBLINS, YOU DOOFUS!
AND WE WENT TO CHOSHI, SO WHAT
THAT REALLY MEANS
IS I SAVED TWO CITIES!
(BOTH GROANING)
[MINORI] I'M SO GLAD YOU MADE IT
BACK SHIROE. GOOD TO SEE YOU!
HMMPH.
[SHIROE] IT'S GREAT TO SEE
EVERYBODY. (ALL CHUCKLING)
[NYANTA] WELL, NOW... IT'S
BEEN FAR TOO LONG MY MAN...
I'M GLAD TO SEE YOUR FACE.
WHY DON'T WE BREAK THIS UP WHILE
HE STILL HAS BOTH HIS ARMS?
SO, WHO'S YOUR
LITTLE FRIEND HERE?!
[NAOTSUGU]
UWALLH... I'M JU... AH!
[TETORA] I'M A STAR SHINING
IN THE EVENING SKY!
MY NAME'S TETORA. THE ORTHODOX
GALAXY STYLE STARLET!
BUT FEEL FREE TO
JUST CALL ME TETORA!
A STARLET, HUH? OKAY WELL...!
I'M A GUILD MASTER!
(NAOTSUGU CRYING OUT)
[TETORA] ZAP! ZAPPITY‐ZAP! ZAP!
I AM NOT GONNA MESS WITH THAT
RIGHT NOW. [TOYA] NO DOUBT.
[SHIROE] I THINK WE'LL SAVE THE
FORMAL INTRODUCTION
FOR LATER. HUH?
[MINORI]
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
WELL, UH... UH?
YOU'RE HERE. RIGHT
ON TIME AS USUAL.
HEY NOW, DID YOU GROW?
MY LORD THAT'S
NOT VERY NICE!
UH... S‐SORRY! I MEAN, IT'S
JUST YOU'RE STANDING TALLER!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
SHE SEEMS... DIFFERENT...
THAN THE LAST TIME I SAW HER.
(EXHALE)
DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT
MY LORD, IT'S EMBARRASSING.
UH... I'M SORRY! SORRY!
[SHIROE, THINKING] I FORGOT...
SHE'S BEEN THROUGH
A BATTLE OF HER OWN.
AND NOT JUST HER, THEY ALL HAVE.
[SHIROE, VOICEOVER] NO MATTER
HOW CLOSE THEY ARE...
NO MATTER HOW FAR AWAY...
THE DISTANCE MEANS NOTHING...
THEY'RE ALL WORKING TO MAKE
THEIR OWN PART OF THIS WORLD
THE BEST THEY CAN.
I'VE GOT A LOT OF FRIENDS,
AND WE'RE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
[SHIROE]
IT'S GOOD TO BE HOME, AKATSUKI.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE
YOU BACK, MY LORD.
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER]
VALENTINE'S DAY ALSO COMES TO
THE WORLD OF ELDER TALES.
IT'S HERE. YOU CAN
IGNORE IT IF YOU WANT,
BUT IT'S RIGHT HERE
ON TOP OF US.
SOME WILL FIND HAPPINESS,
AND OTHER...? WELL...
SOMETIMES IT CAN BE DIFFICULT TO
KNOW WHAT'S IN ANOTHER'S HEART.
WHO DO YOU LOVE?
[SHIROE] I WANT TO STAND UP...
ONE MORE TIME...