[SHIROE] WELL YEAH, THAT
CERTAINLY IS SURPRISING.
[NYANTA, VOICE CHAT] RUNNING
INTO KAZUHIKO LIKE THAT
WAS INDEED UNEXPECTED, HUH.
THIS TOWN HERE SEEMS TO HAVE
BECOME QUITE
THE NEXUS OF PLOTS
AND SCHEMES.
AND A LOT OF INNOCENT FOLKS
HAVE PAID THE PRICE.
[SHIROE, VOICE CHAT] SO HOW ARE
MINORI AND THE OTHERS...?
[NYANTA] THEY'RE OUT OF DANGER,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN...
(ASTONISHED BREATHS)
(DISTRAUGHT)
(SNIFFLING AND CRYING)
MPH.
[TOYA, THINKING] HE WOULDN'T
LISTEN... HE JUST WOULDN'T!
[MINORI, THINKING] THE TOWN'S
IN RUINS... WE LOST...
[SERARA, THINKING] I SURE WASN'T
MUCH HELP OUT THERE...
I'M SORRY.
(EXHALE)
[ROE2] SO I GUESS THIS
IS THE ROAD TO IKOMA.
[MINORI] YEAH.
[SERARA] SO... IT'S TIME
FOR YOU TO GO?
[ROE2] THAT'S MY BEST
CHANCE FOR MAKING FRIENDS
WITH THE SUNLIGHT AGAIN.
OF COURSE, WHO KNOWS WHAT
THE FUTURE HOLDS, RIGHT?
[ROE2] OH, HANG ON...
[MINORI] HM?
[ROE2] I'VE GOT SOMETHING FOR
YOUR...
TEACHER, I THINK YOU SAID.
I NEED YOU TO GIVE THIS TO HIM.
[MINORI] MASTER SHIROE?
YES.
BUT WAIT...
[ROE2] HMM?
[MINORI] OH...
I MEAN, UH,
SURE I'LL TAKE IT.
ALRIGHTY THEN,
IT'S TIME TO HIT THE ROAD.
IT'S A REALLY NICE DAY OUTSIDE.
MAYBE TOO NICE, IF
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
[ROE2] UH...? OH?
WELL THAT WAS NICE OF YOU.
(DISAPPOINTED SIGHS)
[ROE2] HEY GUYS, COULD YOU CALL
ME "BIG SISTER" ONCE MORE?
[SERARA, SNIFFLING] GOODBYE,
BIG SIS! I'LL MISS YOU!
[ROE2] OH, HEHE,
THAT FEELS GOOD!
[TOYA] BIG SISTER...
SISTER ROE2...
GOODBYE, BIG SIS.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, BIG SIS.
MM‐HM!
[ROE2] WE'RE GONNA
SEE EACH OTHER AGAIN,
MY LITTLE BROTHERS AND
SISTERS! I PROMISE!
[TOYA] HM. I GUESS THAT'S THAT.
[DARIELLA] AND NOW, I MUST GO
ALTHOUGH
IT'S DIFFICULT TO SAY GOODBYE.
[TOYA] OOH?
[DARIELLA] I'LL BE MEETING
UP WITH SOME PEOPLE I KNOW
IN SANAL AND FINISH
MY TRIP FROM THERE.
[TOYA]
UHH...
IT WAS NICE TO MEET YOU...
AND GET TO KNOW ALL OF YOU.
I REALLY DO HOPE WE CROSS
PATHS SOMETIME AGAIN.
[MINORI] YES... WE'D LIKE
TO SEE YOU TOO, DARIELLA.
[TOYA] UNGH.
HMPH.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY
WITH JUST LETTING HER GO?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU KNOW, MISS DARIELLA?
YEAH, WELL...
MMM...
[TOYA] IT'S OKAY, REALLY.
[RUDY] ALL RIGHT...
ONE THING THOUGH, I
KNOW IT'S KINDA WEIRD...
HER HANDS, HER FINGERNAILS
WERE RAGGED...
LIKE SHE'S BEEN WORRIED
AND BITING THEM.
IS THAT SO?
[RUDY, THINKING] HE MUST HAVE
REALLY HAD AN EYE ON HER.
I GUESS THAT MEANS TOYA'S THE
ONLY ONE OF US TO REALLY NOTICE
SHE WAS HIDING SO MUCH PAIN
BEHIND THAT SMILE OF HERS.
SO TELL ME...
DO YOU BITE YOUR
FINGERNAILS TOO?
HUH? WELL NOW THAT YOU MENTIONED
IT... NOT SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE.
WELL, I'M GLAD
TO HEAR IT.
YOU GOT SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND?
I'M PRETTY EASY TO TALK TO.
JUST SPIT IT OUT,
GET IT OFF YOUR CHEST.
(LAUGHS) OH, TOYA...!
COMPANION OF MINE...
DON'T BE BASHFUL. YOU CAN ALWAYS
COME TO RUNDELLHAUS FOR ADVICE.
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT?
ROMANCE, OF COURSE!
HUH? (SNIGGERING)
DON'T THINK SO.
YOU'VE BEEN HAVING YOUR OWN
PROBLEMS LATELY, BUD.
THANKS, BUT NO THANKS.
BUT I'M AWESOME!
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING TOGETHER)
[LOREILE] UH...
PRINCESS NUREHA! WELCOME BACK.
I WAS BEGINNING TO
WORRY ABOUT YOU.
(SIGH)
(HALF‐LAUGH)
(SHOUTING DIRECTIONS)
[ISUZU] DON'T YOU THINK
WE SHOULD GET IN THERE
AND HELP THEM OUT, GUYS?
[MINORI] MM‐HM... YEAH,
THAT'S PROBABLY A GOOD IDEA.
WE COULD CERTAINLY HELP WITH
THE HEAVY LIFTING YOU KNOW?
[RUDY] NOW WAIT, WE'VE ALREADY
ACQUIRED OUR WYVERN HIDE,
BUT WE NEED TO GET THE
REST ON THE WAY BACK HOME.
WE DID WHAT WE SET
OUT TO DO HERE,
WE SHOULD REALLY GET GOING.
[TOYA] COME ON! WE CAN'T JUST
LEAVE THE PLACE LIKE THIS.
[RUDY] THEY'RE FINE, TRUST ME!
REMEMBER THIS IS AN
IMPORTANT DESTINATION!
THEY'LL BE UP AND
RUNNING SOON ENOUGH!
WELL NOW, IT MIGHT BE OKAY.
IT DOESN'T REALLY LOOK LIKE
THEY'RE HANGING THEIR HEADS
OR ANYTHING.
[RUDY] THEY'RE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
THEY'RE USED TO
THIS SORT OF THING.
RUDY, DON'T YOU THINK
IT'D BE A NICE THING
IF WE WENT OVER THERE
AND HELPED OUT...?
THEY LOOK LIKE THEY
COULD USE US, YOU KNOW?
OH NO! DON'T EVEN
WORRY ABOUT IT!
THEY'LL PROBABLY GET HELP
FROM A NEIGHBORING TOWN.
HOW DO I PUT THIS...?
IN THIS KINDA SITUATION,
IT CAN MAYBE GET A LITTLE
UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH OUTSIDERS HANGING AROUND.
[SERARA] HMMM...
I DON'T KNOW... ARE
YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
ARE YOU SAYING THAT
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
SHOULD BE TAKING CARE
OF THEIR OWN PROBLEMS?
LOOK CAN WE PLEASE JUST
LET IT GO? TRUST ME...
THEY CAN HANDLE IT ON THEIR OWN.
[ALL] OHHH...?
[TOYA] OKAY, I GUESS YOU WOULD
KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
YEAH...
(STREET CHATTER)
[CAMUS] MY DEARS...! OUR MEETING
WAS FORETOLD IN THE STARS!
[GIRL A] UUHH...
WAS THAT SUPPOSED
TO BE A PICKUP LINE?
[GIRL B] I THINK IT
WAS... SUPER CREEPY.
[CAMUS] MY HEART DANCES WITH
JOY! WON'T YOU BE MY BRIDE?
[AKATSUKI] SO WHERE DO YOU
WANT TO GET BURGERS TODAY?
OR WOULD YOU RATHER STOP
OFF FOR FRIED RICE BALLS?
[TETORA] OH, COME ONE! WE'RE NOT
GOING TO EAT THAT FATTY
JUNK AGAIN ARE WE?!
THAT'S CORRECT...
AND WE NEED TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
WE'RE GONNA DO FOR DINNER...
IT'LL BE HERE BEFORE
YOU KNOW IT.
LOOK, I DON'T MIND
ORDERING FOOD
OR EATING OUT
SOMETIMES, BUUUTT...
IF NYANTA WERE HERE
COOKING FOR US,
I BET OUR DIETS WOULD
BE MUCH MORE BALANCED!
I CAN'T AFFORD TO HAVE PIMPLES!
A STARLET'S COMPLEXION
IS SO IMPORTANT,
THE UNIVERSE IS
DEPENDING ON MY BEAUTY!
WELL IF YOU HAVE ABILITY TO MAKE
UP NONSENSE, YOUR MAJESTY...
MAYBE PUT THAT CREATIVITY
INTO COOKING FOR YOURSELF.
I DUNNO. YOU DO
REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN WE TRIED OUR HAND
IN THE KITCHEN, RIGHT?
(GIRLY SCREAM)
(FORCED CHUCKLING)
STARLETS SHOULDN'T
PREPARE ANYTHING
OTHER THAN PASTRIES AND SWEETS!
[NAOTSUGU] YOU ARE SUCH A LITTLE
SNOT! JEEZ! [MAN A] HEY!
[MAN A] OOF!
[NAOTSUGU]
DUDE, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
SORRY MAN, I DIDN'T...
I DIDN'T HURT YOU, DID I?
NGH! NO, I'M FINE, OKAY?
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[GIRLS] UH...
THE POOR GUY, HE MUST
HAVE BEEN JEALOUS
OF HOW HAPPY
WE ARE TOGETHER!
ISN'T THAT
RIGHT, HONEY?!
YOU KNOW I GOTTA TELL YA,
I'VE BEEN SEEING
A LOT OF THAT...
PEOPLE SEEM ON EDGE
AND FRUSTRATED LATELY.
[TETORA] HUH?
YEAH, I'VE SEEN IT, TOO.
IT REMINDS ME OF WHEN
WE FIRST GOT HERE.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE LIKE THAT.
EVERYONE WAS LOST AND CONFUSED
AND AS A RESULT,
PEOPLE FELL APART AND GOT DOWN.
THERE WAS MASS DEPRESSION.
HEY! DON'T YOU THINK YOU'RE
EXAGGERATING A LITTLE.
YEAH, LOOK! THOSE PEOPLE OVER
THERE SEEM PRETTY GIDDY TO ME!
(GIGGLES)
SEE HOW HAPPY THEY ARE. COME ON!
YEAH! NAOTSUGU SAYS HE ONLY
LIKES TO THINK OF PANTIES,
BUT DEEP DOWN INSIDE
YOU'RE A BIG OL' TEDDY
BEAR! AREN'TCHA BOY?!
[NAOTSUGU] WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
[TETORA] PANTIES.
COME ON! WHAT WAS THAT?!
THAT'S A HUGE DOUBLE STANDARD
IF SHE GET TO SAY PANTI‐
ARRRGGH!
[NAOTSUGU, STRAINING]
BUT SHE SAID IT TOO!
MY FREAKIN' JAW...
THAT HURT! HUH?
[NAOTSUGU, THINKING] YOU THINK
WE'RE "EXAGGERATING," HUH?
WELL I HOPE SO.
BUT IF THIS SAME KIND
OF MASS DEPRESSION
IS SPREADING THROUGH
AKIHABARA RIGHT NOW,
THEN IT MIGHT BE EVEN
WORSE THAN LAST TIME.
WE COULD BE IN REAL TROUBLE.
THEN DON'T STAND THERE AND
LECTURE ME ABOUT OTHER
PEOPLE'S WARS WHEN THEY'RE
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF US!
THEY TAKE SOMETHING FROM
ME, I TAKE FROM THEM.
IT'S AN EVEN TRADE.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
LONDARK'S TOUGH.
BUT I GUESS EVERYONE
HAS THEIR LIMITS.
MORE AND MORE OF US
ARE STARTING TO FEEL
LIKE WE'RE VICTIMS IN ALL THIS.
PEOPLE ARE HAVING PROBLEMS
ADJUSTING TO THIS WORLD.
[EINS] OUR SOCIETY IS FAVORING
CERTAIN PEOPLE OVER OTHERS.
THE RICH STAY RICH,
AND THE POOR STARVE.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
SO NOW WE HAVE ADVENTURERS
ACTUALLY JOINING UP WITH PEOPLE
OF THE LAND
WHO WANT TO GO TO WAR.
SOMETIMES, THEY'RE EVEN
INSTIGATING IT.
UH... THIS ISN'T GOOD.
[SHIROE, THINKING] I THOUGHT
IT WOULD NEVER COME TO THAT.
AT LEAST, NOT FROM THE
ADVENTURER SIDE
OF THINGS ANYWAY.
AND IF THE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND DO GET INVOLVED,
WHO KNOWS WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
WAR IS A MUCH MORE
FAMILIAR THING TO THEM.
MOST OF US WERE BORN IN A
PEACEFUL AND ORGANIZED JAPAN.
AND IF ALL THOSE DIFFERENT
FACTIONS WERE TO GO TO WAR,
WOULD WE BE ABLE TO DO THE RIGHT
THINGS, AND KEEP OUR DISTANCE?
[SHIROE] OH MAN, WHY THE HELL
CAN'T THIS JUST BE A QUEST?!
(SIGH) GIVE ME A
BUNCH OF MONSTERS
OR A RAID BOSS TO FIGHT
AGAINST ANY DAY!
[SHIROE, THINKING] SO IF WAR
BREAKS OUT AMONG ADVENTURERS
OR WITH THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND,
WHAT CAN THE ROUND TABLE
CONFERENCE DO ABOUT IT?
WE'RE IN PRETTY LOUSY
SHAPE RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE STILL HAVING A HARD TIME
WITHOUT KRUSTY.
I JUST HOPE WE GET SOMETHING
POSITIVE OUT
OF ISAAC'S TRAINING PROGRAM.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
[ISAAC] COME ON! GET THE
LEAD OUT, YOU PANSIES!
THIS IS RIDICULOUS,
A LITTLE BIT OF TRAINING
AND THEY'RE GIVING UP.
[REZARICK] NOT SURE
IT CAN'T BE HELPED...
PEOPLE OF THE LAND JUST DON'T
HAVE A LOT OF
STAMINA TO SPEAK OF.
THIS SUCKS.
VILLAIN IN GLASSES,
YOU'RE WASTING OUR
TIME ON THIS‐! HUH?
HEY! REZARICK,
KEEP AN EYE OUT!
[REZARICK] MISTER ISAAC?
[ITHERUS] MASTER ISAAC!
[REZARICK] HM...
[ITHERUS] HUH? OH...
MASTER ISAAC...
[NAZNA] SO DO WE KNOW EXACTLY
WHY SARA WAS KIDNAPPED?
[KAWARA] PROBABLY BECAUSE HE
WANTED TO GET BACK AT US
FOR BEING REJECTED.
[NAZNA]
WHO IS HE ANYWAY?
[OLIVE]
HIS NAME'S CAMUS...
HE'S A COMPLETE SCUMBAG.
HE'S A PERSON OF THE
LAND AND A MERCHANT...
BUT THE THING IS, HE HITS
ON EVERY GIRL HE'S RUN INTO!
[DOLCHE] YOU CAN'T
BE FOR SERIOUS!
THAT LITTLE MINX HASN'T
HIT ON ME YET!
[OLIVE] OH... HEH, SORRY?
ANYWAY, HE TRIED TO HIT
ON ALL OF US EARLIER.
[CAMUS] HEY LADIES...
[GIRLS] HM?
OUR MEETING IS A
BLESSING FROM HEAVEN...
WON'T YOU PLEASE BE MY BRIDES?
(CAMUS LAUGHING)
[ALL] UH... GUH‐ROSS!
[KAWARA] NEEDLESS TO SAY, WE
RAN AWAY FROM OLD CREEPY‐PANTS.
[ISAMI] APPARENTLY HE GOT
REJECTED BY ANOTHER GIRL
IN OUR BRIGADE. THE WHOLE
THING'S A REVENGE PLAY.
[KURINON] THERE'S THAT
PIECE‐A‐CRAP RIGHT THERE!
MPH...
MM.
EH?
DEAD MEAT!
SOMETHING'S STRANGE...
SARA SEEMS OFF.
SHE WOULDN'T BE CAUGHT DEAD
WITH A LOSER LIKE THAT.
[DOLCHE] THIS IS SARA
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
[KURINON] WHATEVER! I AM
GONNA GO KICK HIS ASS! HEY!
[NAZNA] WAIT,
WHAT'RE YOU DOING?!
(PANTING)
YOU BETTER GET AWAY
FROM HER RIGHT NOW
OR I'M GONNA TEAR YOUR HEAD OFF!
OUR MEETING TODAY WAS
FORETOLD IN THE STARS!
[KURINON] OH YOU'RE GONNA
SEE STARS ALL RIGHT! HWAA!
GUH!
OOOH...
WHAT?
WHAT A TOOL.
MARRIAGE GENIUS?
[NAZNA] GOTCHA, SARA!
[DOLCHE] SARA‐GIRL?!
[NAZNA] SHE'LL BE OKAY...
BUT SHE'S GONNA BE OUT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
[CAMUS] HEH...
WOULD YOU... WOULD
YOU BE MY BRIDE?
GAH, I AM GOING TO PUNCH A HOLE
RIGHT IN YOUR DUMB STUPID FACE!
HUH?
(GROWLING)
WOULD YOU PLEASE
BE MINE FOREVER...
[KURINON] YES... PLEASE
MAKE ME... YOURS.
NO WAY! ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
[SOJIRO] STAY AWAY FROM HIM!
[ALL] HUH?
[SOJIRO] HE'S USING SOME
KIND OF SEDUCTION SKILL!
[NAZNA] HEY, SOJI!
[DOLCHE] HEY BABY!
IT'S THINGS LIKE THIS
THAT ARE MAKING ME WONDER
IF IT WAS A MISTAKE TO SHUT DOWN
THE CITY'S MAGIC CIRCLE. HW‐AH.
YOU DECEIVE MY GIRLS... THEN
YOU'RE GONNA ANSWER TO ME.
EHEH... OUR MEETING IS
A BLESSING FROM HEAVEN,
WON'T YOU PLEASE BE MY BRIDE?
[SOJIRO] HUH?
[ALL] UH?
(SCOLDING AND HITTING)
[DOLCHE] YOU DIRTY LITTLE BOY, I
BET YOU LIKE THIS DON'T YOU?!
[SERARA] ALL OF THIS
SURE IS HEAVY, HUH?
IT'S KINDA A SHAME WE DON'T HAVE
A MAGIC BAG TO CARRY IT ALL.
WELL, MAYBE WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO EARN THAT NEXT.
MPH...
[MINORI] YOU DID A GOOD THING
BACK THERE, TOYA. [TOYA] HUH?
WITH THE KNIGHT WHO
KEPT WANTING TO DIE?
[TOYA] THERE'S MORE TO
THAT AND YOU KNOW IT!
YOU HAVE GOT TO BE
ABLE TO SEE THAT!
MISTER, LIFE IS WHAT
YOU MAKE OF IT.
YOU CAN BE ALIVE, BUT DEAD
INSIDE. YOU KNOW IT'S TRUE!
S'NOT EASY TO TELL SOMEONE
WHAT THEY NEED TO HEAR.
I DUNNO... I DON'T
THINK IT HELPED.
[SERARA] I DON'T THINK
THAT'S TRUE AT ALL, TOYA!
[SERARA] OK, MAYBE HE DIDN'T GET
IT THEN, BUT YOU STILL SAID IT.
AND THE NEXT TIME HE FIGHTS,
HE'S GONNA THINK
TWICE, I PROMISE.
[TOYA]
HUH?
YOU GUYS WERE REALLY
GOOD OUT THERE.
MINORI WAS, TOYA
WAS, ISUZU, TOO...
UH... AND RUDY...
I GUESS...
I MEAN... I CAN SEE
EVERYONE GETTING BETTER.
YOU WERE PRETTY
GROWN UP YOURSELF.
(EXHALE) IF THERE'S ONE
THING I'VE LEARNED,
I REALLY NEED TO FOCUS
ON DOING SOME GROWING UP.
IT'S ACTUALLY GOOD THAT I
REALIZED THAT, YOU KNOW?
[RUDY]
OOF. WHEW!
UH... WE'RE WALKING THE REST
OF THE WAY HOME.
MISS ISUZU, WILL YOU BE OKAY?
[ISUZU] OOF! YEAH,
I'LL BE FINE.
IT'S NOT AS FAR AWAY AS I
THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA BE,
SO IT'S ALL GOOD.
HMM. HEY, I HAVE A GREAT
IDEA...
ALL OF THIS STUFF,
MAYBE WE COULD GIVE IT TO
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
YEAH, IT BEATS THROWING
IT AWAY I GUESS.
[ISUZU] OH! UH...
[RUDY] HM?
[WOMAN A] I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
I THOUGHT THEY WERE
HERE TO PROTECT US.
[WOMAN B]
I KNOW, RIGHT? GIMME A BREAK.
I MEAN THEY'RE THE ONES WITH
ALL THE SPECIAL WEAPONS.
[WOMAN A] YEAH, I GUESS WE'LL
HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF OURSELVES.
[WOMAN B] THANKS A
LOT, ADVENTURERS.
UH, NO... IT'S NOT
WHAT YOU THINK...!
I MEAN... THEY WEREN'T
TALKING ABOUT YOU!
[ISUZU] YEAH, I GET IT.
THEY WERE TALKING ABOUT
THE KNIGHTS... BUT STILL...
[RUDY] UH...
GUESS I KNOW WHY YOU
WANTED TO LEAVE...
YOU KNEW THE PEOPLE OF
THE LAND WEREN'T GONNA LIKE
A BUNCH OF ADVENTURERS
AROUND ALL THE TIME.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WERE SAVED,
AND THAT'S BECAUSE THE
ODYSSEY KNIGHTS KEPT
SACRIFICING THEMSELVES.
NOW, I'M SURE THE PEOPLE HERE
THOUGHT THE KNIGHTS WERE GONNA
LEAVE THIS PLACE
BETTER THAN THEY FOUND IT,
BUT THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
[ISUZU] AND SINCE WE WERE
INVOLVED IN THE FIGHT, TOO,
THEY PROBABLY ANGRY WITH US
SINCE WE'RE ADVENTURERS,
JUST LIKE THE KNIGHTS ARE.
[RUDY] YEAH... I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU HAVE TO
APOLOGIZE FOR THEM, RUDY.
APART FROM THE FIGHT...
COMING TO THIS TOWN GAVE ME
A NEW PERSPECTIVE
ON A LOT OF THINGS.
ALL THAT STUFF I WAS
WORRYING ABOUT...
ENDED UP BEING PRETTY
INSIGNIFICANT
ONCE I THOUGHT IT OVER.
(RUDY EXHALES)
[ISUZU] I GUESS THAT'S WHY
I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING FOR
THE PEOPLE IN THIS TOWN...
Y'KNOW, SOMETHING THAT WOULD
HAVE A LASTING EFFECT ON THEM.
WELL, YOU WENT AND CREATED
NUMBER 43,
AND THEY GOT TO BE THE FIRST
PEOPLE TO HEAR A SONG
THAT NEVER EXISTED BEFORE.
AND IT MEANS SO MUCH MORE.
AT IT'S CORE IS HOPE...!
HOPE ITSELF!
WELL THANKS FOR THAT, RUDY.
BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF THAT'LL DO MUCH GOOD...
[RUDY] HMPH...
(BREATH)
[ISUZU] THIS IS
IT... WE'RE DONE.
[MINORI] YEAH, WE ARE...
(BREATH)
[ISUZU] OH...!
(DISTANT SINGING)
[RUDY]
HUH? IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YOU HEAR IT...
WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YEAH, I HEAR IT...!
IT'S YOUR SONG!
(CONFUSED)
[ISUZU] OH...!
OH?
[BOY A]
GOOD JOB! (GIGGLE)
[GIRL C]
AGAIN!
THE KIDS ARE SINGING IT!
(KIDS SINGING)
[RUDY] THIS IS WHAT YOU'VE
DONE, IT'S A GOOD THING.
[ISUZU]
UH...!
YOU GAVE THEIR LIVES
A BRAND NEW SONG.
AND THAT... THAT SONG WILL GIVE
ALL THE KIDS AROUND HERE A LOT
OF HOPE FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
(KIDS GIGGLING)
(ISUZU EXHALES)
(HAPPY SOB)
HM?
(SOB) OH...?
THANK YOU.
(BLOWS NOSE)
[RUDY] AH...!
(SINGING CONTINUES)
[TOYA] EVERYBODY'S JOINING IN!
THEY'RE SINGING IT
OVER HERE, TOO!
[MINORI] THEY REMEMBER IT.
IT'S SOMETHING THEY'RE
GOING TO KEEP WITH THEM.
[SERARA] OH WOW...
[WORKER] NICE WORK!
[SERARA] THIS IS SO AMAZING!
[WORKER] KEEP IT UP GUYS!
[TOYA]
AND THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S GONNA SPREAD AROUND.
AND GO WEST. AND EVENTUALLY,
ALL OVER THE WORLD!
[RUDY, THINKING]
AND THE BEST PART IS
THE FACT THAT WHEN IT SPREADS,
IT'S GONNA GIVE EVERYONE ELSE
OUT THERE SOME HOPE, TOO!
HMPH...
(HUMMING)
(GRIFFON CRYING OUT)
[ALL] HUH?
[TOYA]
A GRIFFON?!
[NYANTA]
GOOD EVENING.
NYANTA! (GASP)
(LAUGH, RUNNING)
[TOYA]
HEY, CHIEF!
[MINORI]
CHIEF NYANTA!
(LAUGHS)
[ISUZU]
CHIEF!
(LAUGHS)
[MINORI, VOICEOVER] GETTING BACK
TO THE CITY WAS REALLY GREAT.
EVERYONE WAS THERE AND
WELCOMED US BACK.
AND AFTER ALL, WE'D BEEN THROUGH
IT MADE US FEEL SO
WANTED AND HAPPY.
IT WAS LIKE A GIANT WEIGHT
HAD BEEN LIFTED.
I FELT RELIEVED.
I COULD BREATH AGAIN.
ALL THE TENSION OF THE LAST
COUPLE OF DAYS DISAPPEARED,
NEVER TO BE SEEN AGAIN.
[ALL] CHEERS!
(LAUGHING AND GIGGLING)
[SHIROE] OH, IT'S GREAT TO SEE
YOU GUYS AGAIN. (LAUGHING)
[ISUZU] I'M SO GLAD TO BE BACK!
[SHIROE]
TELL US, WHAT HAPPENED?
[MINORI, THINKING] AHH...
EVERYONE HERE HAS
ALWAYS BEEN THERE TO PROTECT US
FROM ANYTHING THAT CAME OUR WAY.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT? EVEN
THOUGH WE'VE LEARNED
WE CAN TAKE CARE
OF OURSELVES,
THEY'LL STILL BE HERE. AND
THEY STILL LOOK OUT FOR US.
WE CELEBRATED A LONG
TIME THAT NIGHT,
AND I DON'T KNOW WHEN
WE ACTUALLY GOT TO BED.
BUT ONE THING I DO REMEMBER,
ROE2 CAME TO ME IN A DREAM.
AND EVEN THERE, SHE
WAS STILL A MYSTERY.
(SIGH)
[AKATSUKI, VOICEOVER] MYSTERIOUS
MONSTERS HAVE INFILTRATED
AKIHABARA AND ARE PLUNGING
PEOPLE INTO CHAOS.
THE GENIUSES. WHAT
ARE THEY, EXACTLY?
ROE2'S LETTER HOLDS THE KEY.
AND IN SPITE OF ALL
HIS INVESTIGATIONS,
SHIROE NEVER ANTICIPATED
THEIR ARRIVAL.
THERE ARE PEOPLE OF
THE LAND, ADVENTURERS,
AND NOW... SOMETHING ELSE.
[SHIROE] MY COMRADES
ARE ALWAYS BESIDE ME.