I don't understand how
everything got so screwed up...
I wanted to help her...
I didn't wanna fight.
I wanted to help.
That's it.
That's all there is to it.
Then you'll die.
There's no way you'll
survive this next attack...
Not if you stand there
and take it head-on.
[Music]
Utilization terrain at absolute
coordinates X-228561.
And Y-568714...
Commencing experiment
at 8:30 p.m.
Japan Standard Time...
Subject number 10032.
Test application.
How to cope in combat when
reflection is inapplicable.
That's fine.
But who are you?
That so...? Then what
are you doing here?
"I do not know.
I cannot
comprehend it."...
Well... That is
the answer Misaka
would have given
the strange young man.
I don't understand...
Why is it his face that
comes to Misaka's mind now?
RSPK Syndrome, known to
laymen as "poltergeisting"
refers to the
uncontrollable outburst
of power from a person
who is no longer in
touch with reality...
It occurs as the result
of emotional trauma
or excessive stress.
Here in Academy City,
we conduct experiments
to develop students'
psychic abilities,
using various methods
to separate the
subjects from ordinary,
everyday reality.
Whatever the method used,
once separated from
conventional reality,
esper students create
a reality of their own,
one that is different
from everybody else's.
As a result, they obtain
their specific power,
one that operates on
principles different
from the rest of us.
Using that power, they are
able to warp the very fabric
of their own micro-world
by destroying things
without touching them,
predicting the future by
simply closing their eyes,
teleporting, and so on.
The ability development
program used in Academy City
is designed to create
alternate realities
by exposing students
to certain stimuli.
To put it simply, we use drugs
and the power of suggestion
to bring about a certain
change inside the brain
and encourage
reality creation.
The theory goes
that by assimilating
a certain curriculum,
anyone can
achieve an awakening
of their psychic
abilities...
Well, almost
anyone, at least.
Because there are
still some students
who do not experience
that awakening...
Like Toma, for example.
That's right. Like Kamijo...
Though... in truth,
it's the type of
students like Kamijo
who are the most important
for us to study.
Oh... so then you know
about Toma's power?
Yes, well, that Kamijo has
been a naughty little boy
ever since he enrolled
in classes here...
We've been through
quite a lot together...
quite a lot indeed.
-Another one?
-That stupid jerk.
The fact that
Level Zeroes exist
means that there
are still principles
that we do not
fully understand,
and knowing that may
prove very useful to us...
If we can learn more
about those principles,
they may be the key that
will help us find SYSTEM.
Basically, SYSTEM refers
to one who arrives
at the knowledge of God
while in a mortal body...
Humans can't understand the
whole of the world's truth.
It's assumed that no
mortal can do so...
but, if someone were to
be found or created whose
body was beyond human,
perhaps they would be able to
obtain the divine knowledge
that is beyond
the rest of us.
Obtaining knowledge
of God's truth, huh?
My hand... feels weird.
Must've been knocked
unconscious...
But I can't remember how.
Oh... that's right.
Why are you doing this...?
You're crazy.
You look like you're
about to fall apart...
battered and bruised and
lying on the filthy ground.
I think your heart may
even have stopped
for a second there.
Now this...
How can you smile after
everything that's happened?
Because I have an idea.
A way to force them to
stop the experiment...
I've finally got it.
It's actually pretty simple
when you think about it.
Tree diagram would've
programmed the experiment
with the presupposition
that Accelerator
was the strongest esper
in Academy City, right?
Well... what if
it was wrong...?
What if the
mighty Accelerator
was beaten
easily in a fight
with somebody who's supposed
to be weaker than he is?
No researcher would
continue an experiment
when the basic premise
was proven flawed.
It's so simple...
We just have to convince
the researchers of one thing...
That they were wrong
about Accelerator.
That he's actually
incredibly weak.
Don't you see
that's impossible?
There's no way that
could happen...
I've only come
face-to-face
with Accelerator one time,
but that doesn't matter...
I can tell.
A fight with him isn't a
question of who's going to win
and who's going to lose.
It's a question of how
much punishment
he wants to dish out.
And how much time he wants
to take carving up his opponent.
Besides, don't forget,
I'm a Level 5,
like Accelerator is...
Even if by some miracle,
I did defeat him...
the researchers would
write it off as an anomaly
that's within the
acceptable margin of error.
They wouldn't scrap the
experiment because of that...
They wouldn't believe
he was truly weaker.
In that case...
I suppose I'll have to be
the one who fights him.
What if Academy City's
strongest Level 5...
Was handily defeated in a
fight with Academy City's
weakest Level Zero?
You can't be serious!
It's impossible.
You don't understand how
powerful Accelerator is...!
We're talking
about a guy so strong
he wouldn't even
break a sweat
if he had to defend himself
from an entire army,
and now you want to
fight him head-to-head? !
He can manipulate
kinetic momentum,
thermal quantity,
electric charge,
and any other kind of vector
with nothing
more than a touch.
Any attack you made would
fail to reach him...
He'll just send them all
bouncing back at you!
You would have to be crazy
to take on someone
with that kind of power
and not a single shred
of sportsmanship...!
Especially considering
the shape that you're in!
You'd have no chance
on a good day,
much less as you
are right now!
Don't go.
When I ran into you...
you were on your way to
find Accelerator, weren't you?
So tell me.
Tell me where
I can find him.
The time is 8:25
by my clock.
You're a few
minutes early.
So... I'm assuming
you have no objection
to being my next target
for this experiment?
"No... I am Misaka,
serial number 10032,"...
Misaka identifies herself.
"Before we begin, wouldn't
it be wise for you
to verify my password
to make sure I am part
of the experiment?"
Misaka responsibly advises.
Honestly...
I hate to question you
when you're so diligently
performing your role
in an experiment
to increase my strength...
but you strike me as
unnaturally relaxed...
given the situation.
You sure your mind isn't
occupied with something else?
"The phrase 'something else'
is too vague for me
to fully comprehend,"
Misaka replies in
some confusion.
"Three minutes and
twenty seconds remain
until the experiment
is scheduled to begin.
Are you ready?"...
Misaka inquires,
seeking confirmation.
I don't think
I'll ever understand
how you can be so willing
to throw your life away.
My life is more
important to me
than anything else
in the world...
Which is why my
desire for greater power
will never dissipate
or diminish...
So it doesn't matter if
I've killed ten
or ten thousand in
this experiment.
As long as I'm
getting stronger,
your deaths are nothing to me.
I'll laugh away each kill.
"You say you cannot
understand Misaka,
but Misaka also finds your
behavior confusing,"...
Misaka replies honestly.
"You are already the
strongest Level 5
in Academy City...
You are in a position where
nobody else can touch you...
so there is no need for you
to become more powerful,"...
Misaka states reasonably.
The strongest, huh?
Yeah, that's true...
but how have people arrived
at that evaluation of me...?
They named me the
strongest Level 5
because they actually
fought me and got beat.
That's the basis for my
classification right there.
I'm at the top of the heap
because a bunch of dimwits
thought to themselves,
"Hey, I think I'll pick
a fight with that guy.
It'll be fun to see
what he can really do!"
Well, that's not
good enough...
It's not even
that close...
I've got bigger
plans for myself.
That level of power
is insignificant!
The power I'm after goes
a step beyond that...
I don't want people
thinking that fighting me
would be an
interesting challenge.
I want the very idea of
going up against me
to be unthinkable, something
that nobody would dare!
"One minute thirty seconds until
the experiment commences...
Are you certain that
you are ready to begin?"
Misaka asks, again
seeking confirmation.
I thought we might
be able to kill
a little time before
we got to it...
but this is just hopeless.
There's no point in
trying to hold
a normal conversation
with you.
Okay then, are
you ready...?
It's almost time
for you to die...
you substandard
factory reject.
"The time is 8:29
and 45 seconds...
We will now commence
trial number 10032."
"Will test subject Accelerator
please take his position?"
Misaka instructs politely.
The industrial district
on the west end.
Find the train
yard there...
That's the location of
the ten thousand and
thirty-second testing site.
"Up to now, you have had
contact with one Misaka...
Serial number 10032.
I am that Misaka."
What's the matter, buddy?
Oh, of course...
It's the electromagnetic
waves from my body.
This is insane.
If you really
wanna help them,
you have to let
me try my idea.
The important thing is
for me, a Level Zero,
to defeat Accelerator without
assistance from anybody else...
If I have a Level 5
fighting alongside me,
then it won't
mean anything.
Don't worry.
No matter what, I'll
bring her back with me.
It's not like
I don't get it.
If I were to go
to the train yard,
I wouldn't be able to do
anything to help out...
Still... Does he really think
I can just stay here? !
What is the point of
all this running around?
It doesn't matter how much
time you buy for yourself.
No miracle is gonna
come along and save you.
Have you noticed?
Tonight the wind is at
zero miles per hour.
What's that smell?
Hah...! So that's it.
You're breaking down the
oxygen with electricity
and turning it into ozone.
If you take away my air,
maybe I'll pass out--
is that the idea?
That's very good...!
You clever little thing!
You're really going to
give me a run for my money!
I like this
turn of events,
I guess after ten thousand
of you were killed off,
you were bound to start getting
a little bit crafty, huh?
There is something you
should keep in mind, though.
Once I catch you, this
cute little tactic of yours
is going to
fail spectacularly.
You look rather surprised
to see me. It was simple.
All I did was change the
vector of kinetic momentum
underneath my feet.
Hey... Do you know how
you can hit your opponent
without doing any harm
to your own hands?
It's easy.
Change the direction
of kinetic momentum...
Just direct the
vector at your opponent
the second
that you touch her.
Of course, the
damage she takes
does increase by
a factor of that.
So...
What happens to the experiment
in a situation like this?
I'll tell you what
happens... You step away.
Get away from the
sister right now.
Hey, what's the
big idea...?
You inviting members of the
public to our testing sites now?
Well, damn...
This is irritating....
I didn't budget any time
for silencing outsiders
who discovered
our secret.
Stop talking and move.
Why the hell are you
still standing there?
I thought I told you
to get away from her.
You damn loser!
You must have a pair on
you, talking like that...
We have only seven Level
5 espers in Academy City,
and I'm undeniably
the most powerful one.
Yet you're standing
there calling me a loser?
Okay... You've got guts.
Well then...
I have to admit,
I find you intriguing.
"What is this?"
"What in the world
are you doing here?"
Misaka asks
in utter shock.
You aren't her.
You're the kid sister...
You know... you sure
look a lot like Mikoto.
Hi again...
Thanks for helping
with the drinks
and the fleas yesterday.
You're the one
who found him.
So shouldn't you be the one
who gets to give him a name?
"Misaka is uncertain about
your state of mind
and why you have come here."
"Why would you take such a
risk for somebody like Misaka?
As you have been informed,
reproductions of this
body can be made,
so why are you here?"
Misaka repeats.
"Misakas can be
automatically manufactured
with no more effort than
the push of a single button."
"The bodies are
fabricated...
stocked with
borrowed minds...
This process has
been successfully
completed many times
Stop talking.
I don't care
about the fact
that you can
be manufactured.
And I have a very good
reason for being here:
I'm rescuing you.
There's only one of you
in the whole world, right?
Sorry... but you're
not dying today...
I'm afraid you've still
got a whole mountain
of accounts to settle...
I'm gonna help you
out of this situation.
You just keep
quiet and watch.
Very impressive...
a heroic speech.
Tell me, did you
just come up with that,
or have you been practicing?
However, you
must've realized
that there's a slight
problem with your plan
or did you forget
that I'm here?
Man, you're slow.
Is that the
best you can do?
If so, you don't stand a
chance in hell of beating me.
Come on...! Try!
Still so slow...
Yeah, far too
slow to beat me.
This would be a lot more
entertaining for me
if you were to put up
more of a struggle.
Don't just stand
there like a pig
waiting to be slaughtered.
Well, this is boring.
All right, then.
I think it's about time
we put an end to this.
What? !
Apparently there was flour
inside that container.
And there's no wind
tonight, either.
That could turn this into
a more dangerous situation
that I had anticipated.
Dangerous indeed...
There's quite a lot of
powder floating in the air now.
What if someone happened to
start a fire out here...?
The oxygen's rate of
combustion would be very fast.
Things could get
out of control.
Hey, tell me something...
Have you ever heard
of a certain phenomenon
known as a dust explosion?
They can be quite
devastating.
[Music]
There's only one
of you in the world,
but what can I
do for you...?
I'm so weak I can't even get
near someone like him.
Next time,
"Weakest vs. Strongest."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.