Apparently, the books
that Index memorized
contain magic so evil it
can poison the human mind.
That's the reason
she's being pursued.
And yet... with all
she's facing,
she never asked me
to help her...
What now...?
What do I do now?
[Music]
Perfect Memory Ability"
There's no one here...
What's happening?
Runes.
I engraved them
around this spot
so we could have
a little privacy.
And who the hell are you?
Kaori Kanzaki and
I know who you are.
If possible... I
would like to avoid
giving you my magic name.
And why's that?
It's also my killer name.
So you're like
that other guy...
You're a sorceress.
I'm not going to beat
around the bush...
I would like you to
hand over Index...
and I'd prefer to
avoid violence.
And if I refuse?
Then you'll leave
me no choice.
I will tell you my other
name and then take her.
I'll ask once again.
Are you going to hand
Index over to me...
or do I need to say the
name I've been withholding?
You think I'll
give in to you?
You think I'd
surrender her?
No, not to
someone like you.
I'll ask as many
times as I have to.
With this sword, I wield
the Seven Flashes...
Do you know what
that means...?
I have the power
to kill you
seven times over in
the blink of an eye.
Certain death
is the reason
you should surrender
her to me.
Damn...
She's not exaggerating...
What now?
I still have this.
Stiyl has informed me
about your talent...
From what he tells me,
your right hand
can somehow render
magic ineffective.
But that got
me thinking...
What if you can't touch the
source of the magic...?
Then you're out of
luck, aren't you?
Now what...? Should
I try charging her?
Seven Flashes.
You're going to make me
keep asking aren't you?
You stubborn boy...
I don't understand why
you refuse to give in
when you know
what I can do.
Seven Flashes.
Damn you!
It's not working.
Ultra-thin wires?
She's been using the
movement of her sword
to distract me from
noticing them.
You're not using magic...
Maybe you aren't really
a sorceress after all.
Weren't you listening
earlier...?
Stiyl told me about your
sneaky little power.
So does that mean your
sword isn't a magic weapon?
Magic or not,
I don't carry it
around for decoration.
The Seven Flashes
come first...
but the ultimate attack,
Single Flash,
still awaits you...
and don't forget...
I haven't yet told
you my magic name.
And I truly hope you won't
make me say it, boy...
If it was my choice...
I would never give
that name out again.
What do I do?
Surrender?
I'm sorry what
did you say...?
Speak a little louder
I couldn't hear you.
Shut up.
I was telling you
to shut up...!
I will never surrender
to a heartless monster.
Seven Flashes.
Haven't you had
enough pain already?
You're willing to risk your
life to protect this girl...
What is she to you?
There's something
I wanna know.
Why am I still alive?
If you were gonna kill me,
you could've done it
a dozen times by now.
But you keep
holding back...
You're still human enough to
know right from wrong...
You aren't enjoying
this any more than I am.
You understand why
I'm doing this...
Index is an innocent girl,
and you attacked her...
You tore her up and
left her for dead...
You can't expect me...
to just let you
get away with it.
And that's not all...
Thanks to you and
your friends,
she lost her memory...
Did you know that?
What horrible things did
you have to do to her
to make something
like that happen?
I did try...
I have fought like hell
against you people...
but it wasn't enough...
I'm just a pathetic kid
who can't even save
a single young girl.
A weakling who can do nothing
but watch helplessly
while you drag her away to
do who knows what to her.
But you... you're
stronger than that.
You're no weakling
stuck on the sidelines.
With powers like yours,
you can do anything
you want to do...
You can protect anybody
who needs protecting...
but you choose not to!
You understand nothing.
Nothing at all...
I didn't have any choice.
I'm not doing this
because I want to.
I am only doing the work
that I am required to do...
by Necessarius.
Wait, I know that name...
It's the same branch of
the English church
Index belongs to.
She and I belong to the
same organization...
More importantly, she is
a very dear friend to me.
I know I injured
her badly,
but that was never
my intention.
It was an accident.
I didn't know...
I didn't realize the
Walking Church
had been compromised.
I wouldn't have
attacked so hard
if I'd known she would
get hurt like that...
Never.
Hold on a second...
if you're such good friends,
why would you be
attacking her at all?
I had to attack her in
order to protect her...
Without our help, she's
not going to live much longer.
It's because of her
photographic memory.
But why, what does that
have to do with anything?
It's the reason behind
all that has happened.
This is about her
perfect memory.
About those books she's
always describing.
She says they're
in her head--
that she always
carries them with her.
The capacity of the human
brain is surprisingly small.
So you forget...
You get rid of the
memories you don't need...
Doing so keeps your
brain from overloading.
Forgetting keeps
humans alive......
however... Index
cannot forget.
The number of leaves on
a tree-lined street...
The faces of people crowded
together during rush hour...
The shape of every raindrop
that falls from the sky.
It doesn't take long
before her brain
is so packed full
of trivial memories
that it can't function.
Wait a second...
Explain something.
You say that Index is part of
the same organization as you...
If so, why does
she describe
you and your friend as
evil sorcerers...?
It makes no sense...
or... are you saying that
Index has been lying to me
this whole time?
No. She is telling you what
she believes to be true.
But she doesn't know...
not that we all
work together
as members of Necessarius...
nor the actual reason that
we have to pursue her.
All of it has been
erased from her memory.
So she's just working with
what she does remember.
Her fears are not
unreasonable...
From what she knows, it
makes sense for her
to believe that a magic cabal
is after the library
of grimoires.
Hold on... I don't understand...
Index has a photographic
memory, right?
How is it possible for
someone with her ability
to forget everything that
happened before a year ago?
"Forgetting" isn't the
right way to describe it...
It's more accurate to say
we took her memories from her.
You erased her memory...
How is that possible?
You used magic... But
why do it at all?
You and Index were close.
You even belong to
the same church...
That's what you
said, isn't it?
You consider her a
very dear friend.
That's what you
told me...!
If it's true, how could
you do this to her?
Because I had no other
choice, that's why!
I do it because...
because unless I do,
my friend will die.
A full 85% of Index's
brain is used to store
the hundred and three
thousand grimoires...
As a result, she has
only 15% of her brain
remaining to control
day-to-day functions.
That 15% quickly fills
up with new memories,
and once it's full, her
brain will be overloaded.
That's terrifying, but...
Isn't there another
way to save her?
No, there isn't.
How much time does
she have left?
Index's memory
erasure is conducted
at precise yearly
intervals...
If we do not do it
at that exact time,
the erasure cannot occur.
There are three
days remaining.
Only three?
Don't worry.
The procedure we perform
doesn't hurt her...
And as I've already
explained to you,
if we don't do it,
she will be lost.
So I'll ask you again:
will you turn Index over
to us without forcing me
to speak my magic name...?
If we battle,
you will lose,
and her memory will
still be erased...
She will have no
idea who you are
or what you have
done for her.
Fight me and your
sacrifice will mean nothing...
Trying to help her now is
ultimately an empty gesture.
What the hell do you know? !
It doesn't matter
whether or not
she remembers me
once this is over.
I'll explain since you
clearly don't get it.
I am truly Index's friend,
unlike you...!
Nothing you can say
will change my mind...
For better or worse,
I'm on her side,
and that's how
it's gonna stay...
every single thing you've
said since we started
talking has only
convinced me more.
I don't think you're
telling me everything...
Like why you left her
in the dark on this...
After stealing her memory,
couldn't you still explain
what was happening?
Why not at least try to
tell her what you're doing?
Instead you hunt her
down and frighten her.
When she needed
somebody the most,
you people abandoned her.
Some friend you
turned out to be!
Shut up, you ignorant
little maggot!
You know less
than nothing!
Do you think this is
something we enjoy...?
Stealing her memories over
and over and over again?
You look at Stiyl like he's some
monster from a nightmare...
Well, he's not...
You fight for her
as a friend,
while he must save her life
by pretending to be the enemy.
Do you have any idea
the toll it took on him
to confront you? !
You stay safely cocooned
in your self-righteous rage
while Stiyl
sacrifices everything
to save his friend...
What the hell gives you
the right to judge us? !
I've done
everything I can!
I've tried it all!
I once spent a full
year--spring, summer, fall,
winter--collecting
memories for her.
I wrote them all
down in a diary,
every detail
I could remember,
so she would remember, too.
I just wanted to give her
something to hold on to!
But it was no use...
It didn't work.
We watch her start
over every year...
creating new memories
with new people...
rebuilding the world that
we had to take away......
Only to have every one of those
new memories stolen again...
Knowing that it is
all because of us.
We finally realized we
couldn't take it anymore.
We can't stand beside her,
knowing what we'll have to do.
It's too much to bear!
Don't give me that crap.
Poor you...
That's what this is about:
how much it hurts you.
I didn't hear anything
in your speech
about Index's feelings...
You're ashamed of what you
do and scared of getting hurt.
You let Index pay the
price for your cowardice.
You could tell her
the truth about
what has to be done to her.
Tell her she
won't be alone
and there's no
need to be scared,
because she can
make new memories.
Tell her that the
memories she creates
could be even happier than
the memories she's losing.
Do that...
and she wouldn't have to be
constantly on the run anymore...
It sounds like a simple
enough solution,
don't you think?
So why won't you do it?
What's the real reason you're
hiding everything from her...?
You say it's for her sake,
but I think that's a lie...!
You have the power
to help her,
but you keep her trapped
in the same cycle.
There has to be a reason
you haven't told me...
What are you really
afraid of...?
trying to protect...?
What are you
really doing here?
You're so confident in your
strength as a sorceress,
but if you're so damn
powerful, then why...
Why can't you do
something, for... her....
Are we finished here?
Walk slower; I can't
keep up with you.
Geez, why're you in such
a hurry all the time?
Kuroko, are you
listening to yourself?
You're the one
always going on
about the importance
of sticking to curfew...
Well, if we get there late
it's not gonna be my fault!
Come on, please
wait for me!
What's going on here?
Wow, look at that.
That's a perfectly
smooth cut...
It could be a prank
pulled by some student
with pneumatic
control ability.
Yeah, sure... a prank.
It's a good thing
I'm here, then.
This is a job
for Judgment.
Get back here, Kuroko!
What am I supposed to do
with all these bags...?
Thanks a lot.
What are you looking at?
Is something the matter?
No, it's fine.
Are you awake, Toma?
Where am I?
Ow, that really hurt.
Be careful! You shouldn't
be getting out of bed yet.
The sun is up already,
so that must mean I
slept the whole night...
I don't remember
coming back here...
Hey, what time is it now?
You were out for more
than just one night.
Three whole days.
Really? That long...?..
What happened
that would keep me
unconscious
for three days?
There was something...
Index's memory
erasure is conducted
at precise yearly
intervals.
There are three
days remaining.
You got quiet all
of a sudden...
What's wrong?
Are you in pain?
Oh, no.
That's a good sign...
Index still
remembers me...
That must mean her memories
haven't been erased.
She doesn't seem to be
acting any differently...
So it can't have
happened yet.
It's all right then.
Nothing's all right!
It was horrible...
I didn't know what
happened to you.
Until Komoe told
me you had collapsed
in the middle of the road,
I had no idea
where you were...
She was the one
who found you,
battered and bruised
and unconscious,
and carried you back
here to the apartment.
But I had no clue what was
happening to you out there.
I didn't realize that you were
fighting another sorcerer...
that you were in
trouble because of me...
It's my fault.
It's all my fault...
I couldn't help you,
Toma. I'm so sorry!
What's the deal with
all these bandages?
I look like a mummy...
Don't you think that was
a little bit of overkill?
I figured the more I
bandaged you up,
the quicker you were
going to heal...
Of course, there's no way it'll
be as fast as using magic.
No, probably not...
but personally,
I'm just fine with letting
it heal the normal way.
Toma!
Unbelievable! After
everything that's happened,
you still don't believe
in magic, do you?
I swear you're the most
stubborn guy I've ever met!
Calm down. That
isn't what I meant.
It's not that
I don't believe...
I just don't like
seeing you that way.
It freaks me out when
that other personality
takes over your body.
Okay... I understand.
But I'm awake now,
so it's all right.
What do you mean "awake"?
Well... When the
other voice takes over,
it's like I'm
talking in my sleep.
I sound all cold
and robotic.
John's Pen is useful when
I'm unconscious or badly hurt...
but it's still
kind of scary...
It's not me.
What I'm trying to
say is I can understand
why you don't wanna
see me like that...
I don't want
you to either.
I'm sorry, Index.
It's okay...
dummy.
Now, you should
eat something!
Um... I appreciate
it, but...
I'm not hungry.
Too bad... You have to eat
to regain your strength...
I'm a Sister. I know
how to care for the sick.
Yes... I know...
But right now I'd just
like some quiet time
to myself to, uh...
to meditate.
Is that so...? You don't
want the food I made? ...
Yes?
Maybe Komoe's back.
Excuse me... I live here.
Can I help you
with something?
Kamijo, Index,
are you there...?
I don't know
what's going on,
but you seem to have
some visitors out here.
You again! What are
you doing here? !
Looks like you're in
pretty bad shape...
I don't think you're
going to have much luck
running away
from me this time.
He's right...
Up until now, Index has
been staying ahead of them
fairly easily on her own.
But it'll be a different
story if she's saddled
with someone
who's badly injured.
That's why they
did this to me...
To make it easier
for them to catch her.
What now?
Go away!
Please, I'm
begging you...!
Leave him alone and
I'll go anywhere you want.
I'll do anything
you ask... anything!
Index, no!
Just take me...! I'm the
one you want, aren't I?
But I ask one thing:
I don't want you
hurting Toma anymore!
[Music]
The ceremony that will
erase Index's memories
begins tonight
at twelve o'clock.
But I'm not giving up...
I swear I'll find
some way to save her!
Next time, "Limit."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.