Not again.
They're all dead...
They are dead
because of me.
[Music]
Rotten luck.
Seriously...
Who would've expected a
textbook to cost so much?
It's extortion.
Toma...
What do you think you
would've done with the money
if you hadn't had
to buy that book?
I don't wanna
think about it.
No... An... swer... me!
What could you
have bought?
Yeah, okay,
I get it already.
If I had studied regularly,
I wouldn't have
had to buy a...
Hey... what're
you staring at?
No way. Nobody can eat
thirty-six-hundred yen
worth of ice cream...
even you.
Excuse me...! I haven't
complained even once
about how hot and
uncomfortable I am
in this miserable heat...
And I certainly didn't imply
that I'd use your money
to buy something
for myself.
So why would you suggest
that I was thinking
anything about
buying a bunch
of ice cream?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you were
so uncomfortable out here...
Let's find someplace to
sit inside for a while.
Why should we...?
These robes represent
the lord's protection.
I wear them proudly.
I would never dream
of complaining
about how unwieldy and
suffocating they are...
Apparently, I knew this
chatty nun before the incident
that landed me
in the hospital.
I say "apparently"
for a reason...
I can't remember anything
before the last two weeks.
I'm not entirely
sure why...
but for some reason,
I wanna keep my memory loss
a secret from everyone else.
Everyone...
but most importantly,
I wanna keep this
girl from finding out.
I don't understand,
but somehow...
a part of me remembers
who she is...
Her smiles...
and her tears.
Hey, Toma...! Are you even
paying attention to me...?
I was explaining
that as a nun,
I live a life of austerity.
Therefore, I am
forbidden from indulging
in a tasty treat
like ice cream.
I guess that
settles it then...
I wouldn't want you to
break a rule or anything.
Of course, while all
nuns are told to abstain,
I am still a novice,
so surely they can't expect me
to exhibit perfect
behavior all the time.
Certain allowances must be
made for the younger sisters...
For instance, should
a scoop of ice cream
accidentally fall
into my mouth,
surely no one would expect
me to abstain from eating it.
What choice would I have?
Hey-o!
Sorry to interrupt, Kami.
Looks like you're having
a pretty intense
discussion over there.
Wanna introduce us
to your lady friend?
Huh...?
Ah, c'mon, dude, don't tell
me you don't know her name...
What, is the heat giving
you amnesia or something?
Calm down,
I'm just kidding.
It's not hot enough out
here to boil your brains
unless you combine it
with some serious partying.
Well, man...
you gonna tell us your
little friend's name or not?
Let me guess: is it a dude
dressed up as a chick?
Kinda flat to be a girl,
if you know what I mean.
Geez, guys, there
are some things
you just don't
say out loud...
Sure she's a little on
the small side, but...
Toma...
Gentlemen, I think
you should know
I am a nun of the English
Puritan Church...
If there is anything you
would like to repent,
I will be happy to listen
to your transgressions.
Shakes for me...!
Shakes for me!
Three milkshakes,
and they're all for me!
Thanks for the grub, Kami!
How'd I forget my wallet?
How did all of this
end up being my treat?
My stupid luck.
Toma...! We're over here!
Wow... found a booth...
This is not good...
so not good!
Um... is something wrong?
Ugh...
Er... are you in
some kind of pain?
I ate myself to ruin.
On three, guys...
Ready. One, two, three...!
One, two, three!
Yeah!
Excuse me...
You ate yourself
to ruin...? How?
The hamburgers were
only a hundred yen each.
And on top of that, I had
a bunch of coupons to use.
Before I knew it,
I'd ordered thirty of them.
Overdid it a little...
didn't you?
Uh... sorry,
I didn't mean to, uh...
Comfort food.
Huh?
I need a return
train ticket...
It's six hundred yen.
Okay, so what?
I only have five hundred...
I'm short.
That's a shame, huh?
It was dumb. I bought
too many burgers.
And then I had
to eat them all.
Sorry about that...
Maybe you could borrow the
money you need for a ticket
from a friend
or something.
Oh...! That's a great
idea, thank you.
She is majorly hot!
I need a shot of her.
Uh... why are you
looking at me...?
Do you expect a handout
from a perfect stranger?
It's not much...
Come on.
No way...
I don't go around
handing out money.
Can't even spare
a hundred yen.
Hey, I'm not the one
who wasted all of my travel
money on hamburgers.
A perfect way to speak
to a beautiful priestess
such as her...
You've got a real way
with the ladies, Kami.
Beautiful?
I am beautiful. You
want to give me money.
I don't have any
to give you...!
These guys already
cleaned out my cash.
I can't afford to make
any more loans right now.
And you?
Oh no...! Why's
she asking me?
It's not much.
Nope, sorry, lady.
Don't look at me!
You took my picture.
What...? You're
charging me...?
It was just one picture!
Oh, I see...
The priestesses in this
town like their publicity.
You're wrong...
I'm not a priestess.
Huh...? Look at the
way you're dressed.
It's classic priestess.
That's too bad...
I am a magician.
Oh, you're a magician,
are you...?
I suppose you can
prove it, then...
I wanna hear your specialty,
your sect, your magic name,
and your order name.
But you probably
have no idea
what I'm talking
about, do you?
In that outfit, about the
best you can hope for is
passing yourself off as some
wacky itinerant astrologer
who's between jobs.
Yeah, sure, that's me.
Look, it's simple.
She used to be
a priestess,
but now she's some
kinda magician....
Just take it easy.
That's nice...!
You've changed a lot since
the first time we met,
haven't you, Toma?
Uh... I'm just taking
her at her word.
Why is that
such a big deal?
Why is it a big deal?!
You had to strip
off all my clothes
before you'd believe
I was the real thing.
Huh...? What's she saying about
stripping off her clothes?!
Who're all the
dudes in suits?
And when'd they get here?
I need a hundred
yen, please.
Who are these guys...?
Are they acquaintances
or something?
Yes... they're my teachers.
Those are teachers...?
Seriously?
That's weird.
Why are teachers
tracking down a student
at a fast food restaurant?
What is it...?
Is something wrong?
Did you have to
say that stuff about
taking off all
your clothes...?
We don't want word getting out
that you're staying with me.
Yeah, I guess so...
What's more...
what was I thinking
making friends with people
like those two?
Toma!
Hey, look at this...!
Here!
An abandoned cat... Huh.
So I was thinking...
-Maybe...
-No way.
Hey...! I haven't told you
what I was thinking yet!
We can't keep the cat.
But why not, Toma...?
Sphinx needs a new home.
Why can't we keep him?
The student dorms
don't allow pets,
so there's no way
that Sphinx could...
Hey what're you doing
naming it already?
It's not fair...!
He's mine! He's mine!
I said no, and I mean it.
You see...? You scared him,
and now he's run off.
It's your fault!
How's it my fault?
I heard that there's
a Japanese instrument
that's partially made
out of cat skins...
How could Sphinx
not be scared
with stuff like
that going on?
Well if you wanna go there,
don't the English chase foxes?
Foxhunting is a noble
sport dating back...
What is that?
I can feel magic flows
coming together nearby.
Magic what?
Its color is green...
Its attribute is earth...
Is it a runic formula?
Hey... where are you going?
It feels like someone is
setting up a magic circle.
You go on home without me.
Go on home, she says.
What is she, my mother?
Something seems...
off.
You should know
what's happening...
The runes are designed
to keep people away.
Long time no see, huh...?
Toma Kamijo.
Oh, man...
Who's he?
What...? I don't
even get a hello?
Good. That's the way it
should be between you and me.
Where's Index?
There's no need to
worry about her...
She's just off investigating
a magical force
she discovered, right?
Wow...
What the hell kind
of life was I living...?
Was every day full of
weird sorcery stuff?
So...
was there something
you wanted from me?
Don't take me
lightly, boy...
I could kill you.
Oh, I see...
so that's how it works.
There. That's more like it.
That face is more suited
to our relationship.
We can't start
getting all chummy
just because we happened to
fight on the same side one time.
What's that?
What are you reaching for?
It's a confidential matter.
Huh?!
Take a closer look.
Have you ever heard of
Misawa Prep School...?
It's here in Academy City.
Misawa... yeah, sure.
Okay... There's a young girl
who's being held captive there.
Held captive?!
Apparently, the school's
had some changes...
It has become the base
of a pseudo-religion
that centers around
the worship of science...
We don't know
all the specifics...
What we do know for sure
is that the school's
been taken over.
They are now led by a
bona fide, sorcerer...
Actually, to be
more precise...
an alchemist of the
Zurich school of alchemy.
He's the real deal?
I know...
It sounded like a pretty dubious
story to me at first, too.
Hey... wait a sec.
You're accepting
this too easily.
Not good...
If he realizes I've
lost my memory...
I actually listen
to you for once,
and this is what I get?
Are you one of those people
who always has to have
something to complain about?
Well, whatever...
I don't mind if this
goes more smoothly
than last time around.
The alchemist in question is
known as Aureolus Izzard...
He dropped out
of sight completely
about three years ago.
Wherever he was and whatever
he was doing in that time...
he's suddenly decided
to show his face again.
Why would he do that?
Yes... his motivation is
what has us so concerned.
He's after Deep Blood...
That's the girl
I was talking about,
the one held in the
Misawa Prep School.
Her name is Deep Blood?
The name of her power...
She possesses the ability to
destroy a certain creature.
What creature...?
What are you talking about?
They go by many names...
To put it simply...
I'm talking about vampires.
What?! That's crazy!
You're telling me that
vampires actually exist?
Unfortunately,
not even we sorcerers
are sure of all the details.
Basically, Deep Blood
is how sorcerers refer
to the ability to
kill vampires...
Naturally, in order
to kill these creatures,
you must first make
contact with them...
And if you're going
to make contact,
you wanna make sure you have
something like Deep Blood
at your disposal.
I don't get it...
what are you
trying to tell me?
I have a bit
of a problem...
I've been given an
assignment, you see...
I must stage a raid
on Misawa Prep School
to retrieve Deep Blood.
I wouldn't be nodding so
quickly if I were you...
You'll be coming in
with me, after all.
What?!
Oh, and refusing
isn't an option...
See, if you don't
do as I say,
I'm afraid I'll have to
reconsider allowing Index
to remain with you any longer.
Necessarius is
content for now
to use you as
Index's shackles...
to ensure she doesn't
betray them...
However... if you won't obey,
then you're not
useful anymore.
You're crazy...
You expect me to follow
you blindly... really?
Do what you want.
The decision is yours.
Ah, we're home!
-Listen, Index...
-About earlier...
-I wanted to say...
-I just wanted...
Oh...
go ahead.
No... it's nothing.
So, uh...
what's with your stomach?
This...?
Maybe I ate too much.
It seems like you've gotten
bigger in another way, too...
If you know what I mean.
I am at that
point in life.
All right, young
lady, give it up.
What are you
hiding in there?
I... I'm not hiding
anything at all!
Really...! I swear by our
Father who art in Heaven.
On my honor as a sister,
I am not lying to you, Toma.
Wow, your religious
devotion runs deep, huh...?
Now get that dumb cat
out of here immediately!
Sphinxy!
Hey!
Back off... You
know perfectly well
that my robes are
a Walking Church.
So what if they are?
In the name of the Lord,
a church offers
salvation to sheep
who have been separated
from their flock.
And so... this church shall take
the cat Sphinx into its fold,
for he had been lost...
Amen.
Yeah... well, is that church
also gonna provide him
with food and kitty litter?
You just shut up...!
Sphinx is going to
stay here with us.
I don't care what you say!
You can't just
decide that.
There are things
to consider!
I'll take care of
it all, you'll see!
Why... you little...!
Fine. I can see
I've lost this one.
Ah... Divine Father,
you are indeed merciful...
I give you thanks, for
the light of your grace
has finally touched
the soul of this savage,
unfeeling, cold-hearted boy.
Hey, now...
Oh... I almost forgot...
You were going to tell me
something, weren't you?
Oh... right, I was...
It's just... I left
my textbook somewhere
when we were out earlier.
I need to go look for it,
so will you keep
an eye on things?
Yep...
Sure will.
Sweet boy!
One more thing...
Keep the cat
in here, okay?
Uh-huh.
You're a good
kitty, Sphinx...
Yes you are!
What're you
doing with those?
I thought I'd leave her
with some protection.
Innocentius should
do the trick.
Who knows what could happen
while we're off on this
little errand of ours...?
If we're not careful, some
other sorcerers could show up
and try to take Index
away from here...
She can really
be a handful.
Do you... have a
thing for Index?
What?! Of all the
stupid things to ask...!
No...! She's just someone I like
to look out for, that's it...
She's my friend, of
course I care about her.
But not... like that.
Okay then.
I don't know how
I felt about Index
or what she was to me
before I lost my memory...
At this point,
I have no choice
but to keep trying my best
to act like who I was before.
It's almost like
there are two of me.
Yeah... that's some
rotten luck for you.
So this is Misawa Prep?
I gotta say... it doesn't
look too sinister.
It doesn't need to...
That isn't the point.
Hm?
It looks fine...
but the building itself
forms a powerful barrier
that was created
by the alchemist.
So, he's really strong... huh?
Aureolus Izzard
is quite strong...
He's descended from
the great Peraclesus...
I'm guessing you don't know
very much about alchemists,
though, do you?
Well, supposedly they
turn lead into gold...
and they brew
elixirs of immortality
and stuff, too, right?
Yeah, that about covers it....
except... for one more
important thing...
Throughout history,
alchemists have shared
one ultimate goal.
They all seek the power
to manipulate reality.
What's that mean?
Imagine if you
could take anything
you could dream up in your head,
anything at all,
and make it reality...
It's like that.
Huh...? Seriously...?
Anything I imagine
could become real...?
How could anyone hope
to fight against that?
Getting scared now...?
I bet you'd like to just wait
out here and keep watch.
That's too bad.
I need your help...
And in order to help,
you'll need to
know ahead of time
what Deep Blood looks like
so you'll recognize her...
Here. To be honest,
I don't have an especially
good memory for faces.
Her name is Aisa Himegami.
Or so I'm told.
You're kidding...
That's her?
All right...
It looks normal to me.
Of course it does...
Remember, on the surface
they're operating as a
college prep school.
Hey... look.
See that...?
What is it?
A robot...? Looks
like it's broken.
Well, we're here...
Let's not waste
any more time...
and it isn't a good idea
to stay in one location.
Oh...
I guess I can't blame
you for being curious.
You don't see
this too often.
I see robots all the time.
They're everywhere here.
What're you talking about?
That's no robot...
It's a corpse.
[Music]
The alchemist and his scheme
await us inside the school...
Also inside is
Aisa Himegami...
but what is her
true objective?
Next time, "Ars Magna."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.