While out to lunch I met
a strange
priestess-slash-magician.. .
Later I learned that
this young girl
was being held captive
within Misawa Prep School...
The sorcerer Stiyl
basically ordered me
to come with him to
retrieve her...
Everything seemed normal
inside the school, until...
That's no robot...
It's a corpse.
[Music]
Ars Magna
(Golden Transmutation)"
A corpse?
Probably one of the Knights of
the Roman Catholic Church...
Judging by this, I'd say
they've been wiped out.
Why'd he die?
This school is
a battlefield...
and dying's pretty much what
happens on a battlefield.
It's not surprising.
Why is everyone here acting
like it didn't even happen?
Megumi! Wait for me.
She just walked
right through it.
There are two sides:
heads and tails...
Like a coin.
We're in the same
place as they are,
but there's a
barrier between us.
The students are on
the heads side,
and they can't see people
on the tails side, like us.
And while we can see them,
we can't interfere
with them in any way.
Don't bother.
The only way to bring
the barrier down
is to eliminate the core of
the sorcery that made it...
I'll bet the core
itself is located
somewhere outside
the barrier.
This death gives us
another reason to fight.
Why can't we take
the elevator
instead of hauling ourselves
up all these stairs?
We're on the tails side,
remember...?
And the button to
call the elevator
is over on the heads side.
I wonder how cell
phone calls work then.
Huh?
Nothing, really...
I was just curious whether or
not a call made from this side
would make it through
to the other side.
Well then, why don't
you give it a try?
I think I will.
Ah...! This is, um,
Index Libror--uh...
I mean, you've reached
the Kamijo residence... so...
hello.
Wow, awesome greeting...
Have you used a
phone before...
or just this once?
Hey... hold on...
that sounds like
Toma's voice.
What is it...? What
could be so important
that you would use
a cellular phone?
A device known to cause
brain tumors, depression,
and decreased
mental function.
Um... it's nothing major.
Oh, by the way, there were
two servings of lasagna
in the refrigerator.
Did one belong to you?
Why, did you eat
both of them? !
Uh... there was some
pudding sitting in there
with the lasagna, too.
Was...? Don't tell me.
You ate all that,
too, didn't you...?!
Admit it!
Eh, it's okay.
Anyway, I was just
checking cell reception...
I gotta go.
Oh, one more thing...
They say every minute
you spend on the phone
decreases your
life expectancy.
What...? Is there
something wrong?
Oh, no...
I was just thinking that
you seem to be awfully relaxed.
I mean, here we are
in enemy territory...
and almost the
first thing you do
is start chatting up a girl.
I don't really care
if that ego of yours
ends up being
the death of you.
You can get yourself
killed, for all I care.
But...
I don't want you dragging
me down with you, got it?
Jealous, are we?
Don't be ridiculous...
I have already explained
to you the nature
of my relationship
with Index...
I'd think you of all
people would understand.
Just think about it.
She's lived for years
in a body that would be
destroyed without
regular memory erasure.
There have been a number
of people in her life
who were in the same
place as you...
Over the years, these
people have tried to play
various roles for her...
Father, brother,
friend, teacher.
I tried once and failed...
Then you tried and
ended up saving her.
That's all.
That's the only difference
there is between you and me.
He's wrong...
I'm not the one who
saved Index anymore.
I'm not the
person she wants.
He disappeared
when I lost my memory.
Isn't that dress
just the worst?
Yeah, it totally is.
This is my first time
seeing a scientific cult,
but it seems
pretty normal, huh?
Wanna stop by
on the way home?
I was expecting to see
life-size pictures
of the founder on display.
Doesn't give off a
battlefield vibe to me.
Well, that's a bit odd.
There's nothing
to worry about...
Remember, we're on
different sides of the coin.
There's no way
they can see us.
The seraph's wings shine
with a brilliant light.
In the whiteness
of the radiant light,
all guilt will be exposed.
The whiteness is a
symbol of purity.
Purification
requires action.
Action is the present
and the future.
The future is time.
We seem to have
tripped an alarm.
What?
They should be prevented
from even seeing us
because of the barrier.
But something's alerted
them to our presence.
Guilt is the
province of humanity.
Humans fear guilt, though to
experience such fear is a sin.
Sin is a virus that
destroys the self.
You may try to
hide your sin,
but if anything
vile lies within you,
the light of
the seraph's wings
will expose it for all
around you to see...
It will be expelled
from within.
Okay, Imagine Breaker.
Looks like you're up!
Hey wait!
Great.
Why are you running?
Your right hand was strong
enough to protect
you from Dragon's Breath,
but instead of using
it to defend yourself,
you're showing
them your back.
You don't really have
room to talk here...
Anyway, did you see how
many of them there are?
I can't fight all of
them with one hand.
Yeah, fine.
But with a Gregorian
Choir after us,
we need to figure
something out quickly.
It would help if I knew
what this choir thingy was.
I'll summarize.
Essentially, it's a big
spell formed by the voices
of three-thousand-three-
hundred-and-thirty-three monks
in a holy shrine.
Can a bunch of people
chanting nonsense
do anything
that would hurt us?
It sure can, but
it doesn't work
unless every person in
the Choir is speaking
the exact same words
at the exact same time.
We have to find
whatever it is
that keeps them
all synchronized.
I do have one
thing up my sleeve
for a situation
such as this.
Great, then
use it already!
All right.
What was that for? !
Sorry, you drew
the short straw.
Flames will punish
those who are guilty...
Purgatory is the realm
of the purifying flame.
Purgatory was created to
burn sin from the sinner.
Only a purified
soul may pass
through the gates of heaven.
Pain is necessary
for purification......
Pain is an affirmation.
Stop talking!
Can't you see
what's happening to you?
You've got cuts
all over your body!
The inner peace of the
self joins the external
world in a harmonious--
What's going on?
What in the world
just happened?
I have to hand it to him.
The alchemist is one
twisted individual...
Instead of doing the
dirty work himself,
he lets these students
bloody their hands.
Naturally...
I knew that by using a replica
of the Gregorian Choir,
I could lure
you to the core
from wherever you
had been hiding.
Obviously, I expected
someone else to be with you...
Oh well, I
suppose the Choir
must have swallowed up
your plucky sidekick...
Unfortunately for you,
he's tougher than you
give him credit for.
Now then... the great
Aureolus Izzard
has lured me
into his lair.
Why am I here, alchemist...?
What do you want from me?
A little first aid
and she'll be fine.
Really?
Because only the
capillaries were severed
the damage is not as
extensive as it might appear.
It would be far
worse than this
if her arteries
had been cut.
How do you know? It's not
like you're a doctor.
I know more than
most when it comes
to the circulatory system.
You'll need to help me.
-Not cool!
-Collect yourself.
It is just a
medical procedure.
So, what do you think,
Sphinx...?
Where did our Toma
run off to today?
There was some pudding
sitting in there
with the lasagna, too.
Was...? Don't tell me.
You ate all that, too,
didn't you...?! Admit it!
Eh, it's okay.
Something's wrong...
Toma reacted way
too calmly...
He would never be that okay
with me eating his pudding.
Why are these runes here?
We're all done
for now at least.
You did a pretty
incredible job with her.
Are you sure that
you haven't had
any medical
training before?
It's not about training.
Huh? ... Then how did you...?
I told you before,
I'm a magician.
Yeah, I know...
but I haven't seen
you do any magic.
Then let me show
you something.
Here.
See this? It's
my magic wand.
Uh... that's a
police baton!
-The latest model.
-Put it away!
Stop kidding around...
We need to call an
ambulance for her.
You should do that.
It's more complicated
than that...
You need to get
out of here, too.
Aren't you tired of being
cooped up in this place...?
Let's go get
some fresh air.
Actually, I have a
plan of my own...
and it doesn't involve getting
out of this building...
What I need to do requires
me to stay here...
or, rather...
It requires me to stay
with the alchemist,
and for now, that means
being in this school.
Really...? But isn't this
place the headquarters
for some crazy cult?
That was before Aureolus
took things over here.
I'm not a prisoner.
I stay inside
because I do not wish
to venture out....
When I go out
into the world,
I run the risk
of attracting them.
So you're telling me
you're gonna stay hidden
in here forever because
you don't want
the vampires to detect you?
That doesn't sound
like much of a life.
Tell me something...
Do you know what
vampires are like?
They're no different.
Vampires are no different
from normal people.
They laugh, they
sing, they love...
They make sacrifices
for the good of others.
My blood is unusual...
It has a sweet aroma
that attracts vampires...
It rounds them up,
draws them in...
and kills them.
It's the same every time.
It kills every one... always...
without exception.
Academy City is a hub of
supernatural activity...
I thought I could
find someone here
to understand my power...
and then, once it
was understood,
I hoped it could
be taken from me.
But in the end, the solution
that I sought wasn't here.
I don't want to cause
any more death...
If it comes down to it...
I've decided I
will kill myself
before taking another life.
That so...? Then
explain something...
If you're so worried about
the effects of your power...
then why did you go
out to eat earlier?
Simple...
The reason
Aureolus needs me
is because he wants
to attract vampires.
And if I remain inside
the barrier he created,
I cannot draw them out
as he wishes me to.
Okay... but doesn't
doing that for him
go completely against
your objective in all this?
Aureolus made a
promise to me...
He said he wouldn't harm
any vampires that came for me.
He said that he
didn't need to...
He just needed the
vampires' power...
because there was somebody
who he needed to help.
That's why I'm
working with him.
Instead of killing...
my power is helping...
That's the way
I want it to be.
It's never going to work.
Even if he is the kind of
person you say he is...
this is a mistake
that's gone way too far.
If things continue
like this...
before much longer, there
will be no turning back.
Perhaps... but why would
I wish to turn back
from the path I have chosen?
Has he been listening?
I've been here longer
than you think...
and I'm nearer
than you imagine.
Naturally, in
their ignorance,
some lesser minds will doubt
the plans I've made.
Damn you!
You will come no closer,
and your fist will hit
nothing but air.
Oh, yeah? !
What happened...?..
How did you do that?
Now... I find your
company lacking...
-Time to go!
-No!
Are you crazy? !
If she has enough power
to kill vampires...
what else can she do?
When push comes to shove,
you still rely on the
power of your Deep Blood
which implies you do not
wish to give it up.
If you cling to it, how are
you any different from me?
I'm not a killer.
This boy didn't even know
what Deep Blood meant;
he isn't here
because of that.
He only came today
to rescue a stranger
he met over lunch...
Tell me, Aureolus...
what is your true goal?
Do you intend to take an
innocent person's life
because he
inconvenienced you?
If you're the type of man who
would do something like that,
then our arrangement
will end here and now.
I have already made
it clear to you
that I am not afraid
to die if necessary.
Very well...
I cannot afford to waste
more of my time anyway.
Don't be afraid. I have no
intention of killing you.
You will forget everything
that has transpired here.
This is it.
The trail of magical power
leading from the runes
ends abruptly right here.
Where am I?
Judging by the fact
that you're still here,
I'm gonna guess
that we're in Japan.
I have the
disturbing feeling
that I've forgotten
something important...
Know what I mean?
Well... if it really
is important,
I'm sure we'll remember
it eventually.
Do you really think so?
You will forget
everything.
I wanna show
you something.
It's a little trick I know
that will make you
feel better in no time.
Home remedies are
Kanzaki's specialty.
I think I'll just ask
her about it later on.
Just close your eyes...
and then stick
out your tongue.
What?
See?
This is for using
me as a decoy
so your cowardly
butt could run away!
There's a barrier in place
here to keep intruders
from getting away
after they've entered.
Hmm... hello.
Who's there?
You don't remember...?
No, I don't
suppose you would
have any memory of the
name Aureolus Izzard.
Well... that is
for the best.
I consider it
good fortune.
Now, sleep.
Hey. Those look like
the corpse from earlier.
The surviving Knights of
the Roman Catholic Church.
Commence the attack, men.
A Gregorian Choir.
Huh?
A real Gregorian Choir,
not like the
alchemist's replica.
Wait, I'm confused.
You said it took
lots of people
for one of those
Choir things.
Right now, there
are probably
three-thousand-three-
hundred and thirty-three
congregants
offering up prayer
in the Vatican basilica.
Revelation,
Chapter 8, Verse 7...
"The first angel sounded,
and there followed hail
and fire mixed
with blood"...
Hear once more the trumpet
call of the first angel!
That light!
What are these guys doing? !
It's a holy hex
bombardment.
They're attacking it?
But Himegami is
still in there,
not to mention all
those other students!
It's breaking apart!
It's going back up.
Ars Magna.
Ars Magna?
It's the true power
of Aureolus Izzard...
And that's what we're
ultimately going up against.
What are you doing
here, Sphinx?
Don't tell me...
Damn, thought so...
this is part
of Index's robes.
[Music]
Everyone wants a
piece of Index,
including this alchemist...
When he shows the full
strength of his power,
it's going to shake the
very foundation of the city.
Next time, "Deep Blood."
When science and magic cross
paths, a story is born.