The 3rd-ranked esper
in all of Academy City
is a human bug zapper otherwise
known as Mikoto Misaka.
Apparently, we were
acquaintances
before I lost my memory...
Now, I've also met
her younger sister.
The two of them have
me very confused...
I can't help feeling
there's more going on here
than meets the eye.
[Music]
What are you running
away like that for?
Don't get me wrong,
I do appreciate the view.
You've got such
a cute little ass.
Answer me this.
What technique was
it that I just used?
Which of my skills did I
elect to turn against you?
Reflection...
Too bad.... You
were close,
but I'm afraid that's not
this particular technique.
No... The right answer is
vector transformation.
It could be anything:
kinetic energy...
heat... an
electrical charge...
whatever vector comes in
contact with my skin,
I can transform.
In all fairness though,
reflection is
usually my default.
Now then, let's return
to our little match.
Right now, the vector
I'm in contact with
is the heat from
your blood.
Use your imagination
for me...
What d'you suppose
would happen
if I reversed
your blood flow?
Answer the question
correctly,
and then you can rest...
In pieces.
Where is she?
Hey, it's okay, buddy.
I wasn't gone long.
So where did she
wander off to?
Misaka...?! How...?
You there...
You called it in?
If you think
you're up to it,
we'd like you to take us to the
spot where you found the body...
Do you think you
can do that now?
Yeah, let's go.
Hey, kid!
Something the matter?
It's just... this is
where I found her body...
I swear it was right here.
Huh...?
Hey... Uh, yeah.
Sorry kid, there just
isn't anything here.
But there was.
The body of a young
girl was in this alley.
What's going on?
What the hell
is happening...?
I don't--!
Hey, get back here!
What the hell is this?
"I am sorry about this.
It was my intention to
meet back with you after
I completed the operation,"
Misaka apologizes with
complete sincerity.
Hey, hold on...
You are the younger sister
of Misaka, aren't you...?
You're alive...! So what
was that I saw before?
Sorry... I need a minute
to collect myself.
Until a second ago, I
thought I'd found your body.
I guess I was wrong...
I'm glad to know
you're okay.
"No, you were correct
about Misaka's death,
"Misaka calmly reports.
What are you
carrying that bag?
"Before saying more, I must
verify your password,"
Misaka states,
as she was instructed to.
"ZXC-741-ASD-852-QWE-963,"
asks Misaka, testing you.
Uh, what the--?
"It does not appear you are
able to decode the password...
and given that fact,
you are clearly not part
of this experiment,"
Misaka is forced
to evaluate.
What exactly do you
have there in that bag?
"The bag contains
sisters,"
Answers Misaka,
matter-of-factly.
"I must apologize for
leaving the black cat
behind with you,"
Misaka says regretfully.
"But I did not feel
right bringing him...
A battle between humans is
no place for an animal,"...
Misaka justifies
her actions.
"I appear to have
caused undue concern...
That is an unfortunate
result of the experiment,"...
Misaka says, apologizing.
But you truly needn't
have worried...
I came here to explain......
there is nothing amiss.
You see, we are many.
All Misakas
here are Misaka.
What the hell are you? !
"Up to now, you have had
contact with one Misaka...
Serial number 10032.
I am that Misaka.
The Misakas all have
the esper ability
to control electricity...
Additionally, our brainwaves
are all linked
to each other...
Therefore, all Misakas
share the memories
of Misaka 10032,"
Misaka continues to explain.
That's fine...
But who are you?
"We are cellular clones
mass-produced
for military purposes...
The original donor
is Mikoto Misaka,
one of only seven Level 5
espers in Academy City...
We are her sisters,
"Misaka further explains.
Is that so...? Then
what are you doing here?
"We are performing
an experiment,"...
Misaka restates calmly.
"The details
are top-secret,
so I cannot
explain further...
however, it is nothing for you
to be concerned about,"
Misaka continues
reassuringly.
"Please accept my sincere
apologies for provoking
your brief involvement
in this experiment,"...
Misaka requests
with her head bowed.
I'd appreciate it if
you'd look after Dog.
An experiment?
For the military?
More importantly...
what are you doing here
in the first place?
Misaka has a schedule--
It's okay!
Come with me.
That did seem weird.
Is it possible that she
knows about all this?
It all looks delicious!
Indeed.
Since you dropped
by uninvited,
perhaps you would
like to serve.
Go on.... Hop to it, now.
Cook up some yummy
meat for Teacher
like a good little girl.
Very well.
But first, there is
something you should know...
A scary fact concerning
this very meal
we are about to have.
Oh, please...! How could
anything possibly be
scary about this
wonderful meal?
That same meat over which
you are salivating...
Has been proven to
contain carcinogens.
What...? I've never heard
anything about that before.
Where are you getting
your information from?
I see what you're up to!
You're trying to frighten
me away from eating the meat
so you can have
it all to yourself!
It sounds like
we have company.
It's probably just a
door-to-door salesman.
Be a dear, Himegami, and
get rid of him for me
as politely as you can...
While you do that,
I'm going to get this
meat cooked to perfection.
Maybe I'll save you some.
So... so hungry--
What was that...?
Who was at the door, Himegami?
No one... It's
nobody at all.
Have a heart... The least
you can do is feed him...
Just look at
his sweet face.
Toma hasn't seen fit
to come home yet.
I swear, I was just
about to starve to death!
Oh, don't worry...
Feeding one more
mouth is no big deal.
We have a fair
amount of meat,
and we can always fill up on
these lovely vegetables as well.
Fantastic...!
I want meat...!
I want meat...! I want meat!
Next stop,
School District 7...
Tokiwadai Middle
School Student Dorms.
Let's see...
Oh.
So she's in room 208.
Okay...
What are you planning
to say when you see her?
"So, Mikoto, do you
know anything about this
military experiment where
they're killing
off clones of you...?"
Yes?
Um... yeah, hi...
is Misaka there...?
This is Toma... Kamijo.
Hmm... What was that...?
Kamijo, was it?
Ah. No... my mistake...
I must have
the wrong room.
Sorry to bother you!
No, no, it's all right.
I live here, too...
I'm Sissy's roommate.
Oh, are you really?
Yes, I most certainly am!
Hang on...
I've heard that voice
somewhere before.
Hold on...
I think I recognize your
voice from somewhere.
It's you...! You're
the boy Sissy
had a clandestine
meeting with!
Explain yourself! What
do you want with her?
Oh, it's nothing
really that important.
If it's not important,
then why did you make the
trip all the way down here?
You know what...
if she's not
there, never mind.
At this point, Sissy
has not returned home.
If you need to see her so
badly that you showed up here,
why don't you
come in and wait?
This is what the
directory said...
Room 208.
Come in... It's all right;
the door isn't locked.
I'm sorry for
disturbing you--
As I suspected, the
boy from before
Um... yeah that's me.
Have you two been engaging
in extracurricular activities?
No, nothing like that!
That's good to hear...
and you certainly don't
look like you came here
hoping for an amorous
tryst with anybody.
There's no telling how long
you'll be waiting for her.
You might as well have
a seat over on the bed.
Uh, no, thank you.
I couldn't do that...
Not without
her permission.
If that's what you're
worried about, don't bother.
That's my bed.
Then that one
belongs to Misaka?
What are you doing on
somebody else's bed...?
Are you some
kind of pervert?
You're here at an
all-girls dorm
and you call me a pervert?
Everyone has their own
personal preferences.
They may seem strange
to other people,
but that doesn't make
them wrong or perverted.
Come on, like you never
secretly pressed your lips
to your crush's picture...
or stole the seat from
her bicycle to caress.
No I haven't! Ah...
You are crazy...
Is this really what goes
on behind the scenes
at the all-girls' dormitory?
Come to think of it,
if you share a room,
doesn't that make
you classmates...?
The way you keep
calling her Sissy,
it sounds more like a
nickname for an upperclassman.
You were right...
She is older than I am,
though that's not really
why I call her Sissy.
I'm actually a full
year behind her.
Yet you're roommates?
I saw to it that her previous
roommate was reassigned.
Then I took
her place here.
It was simple
enough to do.
It was all totally
legal of course.
Sissy has a lot of enemies
around here, you know...
It's the price she pays
for being powerful...
but I couldn't bear
the idea of someone
as close to her as a
roommate betraying her,
so I felt steps
needed to be taken.
I saw you with
her yesterday...
I believe you when you say
you're not her boyfriend.
So what, then?
Does she have some kind
of quarrel with you?
You wouldn't be
the first person
she didn't get
along with...
Someone with her kind of ability
is bound to make enemies.
Though I would like
it if she had a few more people
to support her.
Support her how?
Is that her out there?
Those footsteps
sound more like...
This isn't good!
The head resident is
here to do a bed check!
What are we
going to do...?
If they find a boy
in the girls' dormitory
at this time of night,
there's going to
be big trouble!
I'll just have to teleport
you outside 'til she's done.
I don't get it.
My power isn't working!
Why doesn't it
work on you?
Well, you see...
There's this thing
about my right hand...
We don't have any
other choice...
Get down there...
You have to hide
underneath the bed!
It won't work.
There's not enough space!
Just do it!
No wonder it's crowded.
Shirai... it's past
time for supper...
Come down to the
dining hall......
Where is Misaka?
Sissy went to her
remedial lesson...
Perhaps it's
running a bit long.
I haven't heard
anything about that...
If she breaks curfew then,
as her roommate,
you will be
punished as well...
Do I make myself
understood?
Yes... I understand, ma'am.
A zipper?
Sisters...
Level 6...
"Based upon the
predictive calculations
made by Tree Diagram,
it has been
established that
only one person has the ability
to reach status Level 6."
"Specific backgrounds
will be prepared,
and a battle
schedule will be set.
Development will be
stimulated by actual combat."
She's been playing me.
Where is she...?
Where would she go?
The propellers are turning, but
there isn't any wind tonight.
The turning
of the propellers
is usually used to
generate electricity.
Then, conversely, couldn't
electricity be used
to make the propellers turn?
There are electromagnetic waves
constantly emanating from her.
So, if I follow the
moving propellers, then...
[Music]
The report I found contains
the shocking truth...
Misaka is pushed
to the breaking point
by her sisters' cruel fate.
If only I could
help somehow.
Next time, "Level 6."
When science and magic cross
paths, a story is born.