It's not fair.
I don't see why you should
have to go back to school today.
Hmm...? Oh, yeah.
I guess that means
you'll be here by
yourself all day.
What, you think
I'll be lonely?
You think I'm some
pathetic little girl
who's going to sit
here pining for you?
We'll sit down together
and figure something out soon.
But for today,
just stay here, okay?
Yeah, okay...
but you'll come
straight home?
Right after school...
and then... we'll find
something fun to do.
Sound good?
All right, then. I'm off.
I'll be waiting!
How should we entertain
ourselves Sphinxy?
Oh no...! We don't have
anything to eat for lunch.
What do I do...? This
is a crisis situation.
[Music]
Zapper looks like
she's in a hurry.
Good morning!
You've got a lot of
energy this early.
You on the other hand,
seem to have none at all.
I guess so...
A lot's been going on.
I'm kind of worn out.
Hey... what're
you saying...?
Was pretending to be my
boyfriend yesterday
that exhausting?
Well, it's not as if
that's the only thing
I've had on my plate lately.
Not the only thing...?!
You're doing the same
thing with someone else?
How many fake
girlfriends do you have?
Huh?
Please! You're the only
person who would ask me
to do something like that
without thinking twice!
You think asking you to
do that was easy for me?
Well. I'll have you know it
was a very difficult decision...
but I didn't have any
other choice at the time.
So I swallowed my pride
and did what I had to do
and that's all there
is to it, you got me?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
I'm sure you're right.
-Well, bye!
-Hey!
Did you actually
hear anything I said? !
Today's September 1st,
the beginning of second term.
Unfortunately, I lost my
memory over summer vacation.
So I feel every bit as
nervous as a new student
would on his first
day of school.
Was that Miss Komoe...?
Hold on...
her feet can't possibly
reach the brakes, right?
True, my feet don't reach
all the way to the pedals,
but I'm still perfectly
able to drive.
Now Kamijo, I hope all
that gawking a moment ago
wasn't because you
doubted my abilities.
Well, I, um...
Wait, is this a pop quiz?
I'm not being graded
on my answer, am I?
Aw, come on. I wouldn't
do that to you.
I like to wait until at
least second period
before giving pop quizzes.
Besides, I've been busy
collecting information.
A friend asked for some
data on AIM diffusion fields.
Never heard of that... AIM?
It stands for "An
Involuntary Movement."...
Basically, an
unmindful action.
The AIM diffusion fields
I was talking about
refer to the power
that espers emit,
kind of like body heat.
At least, in theory...
They're actually so slight
as to be immeasurable.
But if there
was an esper
who could read the
diffusion fields...
They'd be able to detect
any esper nearby...
Am I understanding
you right?
Is that what
you're saying?
Pretty much... And taking
it a step further,
that same esper could
even be able to tell
the type of ability
and how strong it is.
"Yes, this guy
has a battle power
of seventy thousand points."
Or, you know,
something like that...
..At any rate...
there are plenty of people
out there who would love
to have the ability to
detect nearby espers
and measure their power.
Thank you again...
I appreciate all the help.
All right... Tell me
what's goin' on...
Since when do we let
sorcerers sneak in this easily?
Calm yourself.
We are tracking the
intruders' whereabouts.
We should know
before long.
Sherry Cromwell...
She's not some
wandering sorcerer...
She's a member
of Necessarius.
If she's brought
down sloppily,
it'll cause a rift between
Necessarius and Academy City.
How sad to think
of neighbors
who love each other as we
do being so at odds...
Well, so you know,
I'm goin' after Sherry...
If another sorcerer
handles her takedown,
the waves it makes
won't be as big.
There's no need to
involve yourself.
You don't mean...
you're using Kamijo again? !
We'll condense plans
two-thousand eighty-two
through twenty-three-thousand-
seventy-seven.
The Imaginary Number
School District's
Five-Elemental
control method?
This runaway horse could
destroy the world
if we don't act now...
It's best if we take
hold of the reins again
as soon as possible.
Hey...
What's up, Kami?
Somethin' wrong?
-Where's Tsuchimikado?
-Huh...
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen him today.
Know what I think...?
He's somewhere still trying
to finish up his homework.
Yeah... I decided to
conveniently forget mine
so I can see Miss Komoe get
all worked up about it.
Oh, come on.
Okay...! Let's get
homeroom started, everyone.
Before the opening
ceremony begins,
I have some
big news to share!
We have a new
transfer student!
Everybody please join
me in welcoming her!
You heard right; the new
addition is a girl...
So congratulations,
gentlemen...
and better luck to you
next time, little ladies.
Introducing...
Our brand new
second-term student!
-What are you doing? !
-Oh good I found you...
So this is the school
you go to Toma.
I'm glad I picked
the right one!
Oh, dear! How did
you get in here?
You are most certainly not
the new transfer student!
Out you go now.
Out, out, out!
Oh my goodness...!
What were you thinking?
You can't just
march in here,
pretending to be a student!
Take this.
I want you to use that
to get yourself a taxi
and head straight home, okay?
Also, whatever you do, remember
not to talk to strangers,
even if they
offer you candy!
Just so you know...
I'm actually the
transfer student...
I'm Aisa Himegami.
I'm going to faint
from hunger.
I've heard about these ...
I think they
give you tickets
that you can
exchange for food.
Toma makes fun of me for being
ignorant about technology...
but this should be
a piece of cake...
You just put
your money in...
And then you
press the button.
Hey, that's no fair...
There's no button!
Where'd the button go?
What do I do...?
That was all the money I had,
and the machine took it!
Excuse me...
It's simple...
just push the button.
But I don't see any
buttons anywhere on it!
It's a touch screen.
You just have to
press on the monitor.
Well that doesn't
make sense.
You can't touch
the people in the TV.
"Cancel"
Amazing! Do they make
TVs that do that, too?
Not really. Sorry.
Thanks so much...!
What's your name?
You're nice!
Oh, thanks...
I'm Hyoka Kazakiri.
So then, after I
entered the classroom,
I called out Toma's name.
Not only did
he not answer,
the jerk even looked
away from me!
Hmm. I can see how that
would be frustrating,
but only students and teachers
are allowed in the school.
What about you, Hyoka?
You're here.
Oh, I'm here because...
I'm a transfer student.
Okay, then I'll be a
transfer student, too!
About that...
I didn't come here to just
turn around and leave.
I'm not going until
Toma tells me
what I'm supposed
to do about lunch!
Okay... but in that outfit,
you're going to call
attention to yourself.
All right. So what do you
think I should do, then?
Well, um...
I might have one idea...
Come over here a second.
It never ceases
to amaze me.
How can one person get into so
much trouble so frequently?
She's got a real
knack for it.
It stretches well, see...?
And the fabric washes
clean really easily. Amazing!
This is something people
would call "high-tech," right?
I know that voice...
You little idiot!
Hey, Index, you brat!
Just what do you think
you're doing in... here...
uh...
M... my mistake. So sorry.
Toma!!
Today's just the
opening ceremony.
I'll be done by
noon at the latest.
Oh, really? And how do
you know that, exactly?
Because everyone
knows that.
If you know so much,
Toma, then answer me this.
When performing the
ceremony to create
a Telesmatic Image
to be used as an idol
for the English
Church of the Cross,
what role is played
by the direction
and the position
of the caster?
If the calculation's off
by even a little bit,
the spell won't take effect...
but of course you know
the answer, don't you?
After all,
that's how it is.
Everyone knows that.
So, Index, I'm curious...
Who's this girl?
Actually, I don't really know.
But she's my friend.
Yet, you don't
know who she is?
Yeah, so? That doesn't mean
she can't be my friend.
Um, it's nice to meet you.
My name is Hyoka Kazakiri.
Hello. I'm Toma Kamijo.
You're a new student?
Yes... That's right.
That's enough! You're
making Hyoka nervous,
and I won't stand for it!
Don't worry
about him, Hyoka...
Toma may be a hormonally
super-charged teenage boy
who involves himself with
one girl after another...
but he's still a
basically decent guy.
You can hold Sphinx if that'll
make you feel better...
Petting a kitty reduces stress
and lowers blood pressure.
His name is Sphinx?
He's really cute.
I wonder what's wrong.
Animals' senses are
significantly sharper
than humans' are.
Maybe the difference
in our smells
is what's upsetting him.
Kamijo!
The first day
of second term,
and you're already--
Miss Komoe? Shouldn't you be
at the opening ceremony?
I had to come
looking for you.
You're supposed to be
in the gymnasium
with all the other students,
as you know full well...
but here you are
in the cafeteria!
Well, here's the thing...
How is it that you
always have girls
falling into your
lap, Kamijo?
Are you producing some
strange AIM diffusion field?
Why would you
assume that...?
Hey... Kazakiri, could you
please explain why...
Huh?
Did she cut and run
on the first day?
Hey.
Hyoka!
That was quite a
scene back there.
I mean, it... kinda
surprised me.
Komoe wasn't mad
at us or anything.
So there's nothing
to worry about.
If that's true, then why
do you look so sad, Index?
Toma was mad at me.
He wasn't even willing to
listen to what I had to say...
He didn't so much
as smile at me.
What if... What if Toma
doesn't like me anymore?
Now I can tell you
not to worry...
If you can argue like that,
it means you're close.
How's that?
Good friends can argue
with each other
because they know
they'll always be able
to make up afterwards.
I think that's why
he felt comfortable
arguing with you...
because he knows
you're inseparable.
Really? You mean it?
He cares enough
to get mad at you,
and that says a lot
about his feelings.
I'm sure it'll
all blow over.
Though I have to wonder how
he was able to talk to us
with a straight face
after seeing us undressed.
Hey!
Toma!
Well, I'm done. Wanna
go grab some food?
So we're not just eating
lunch at home today?
I promised we'd find
something fun to do.
Wanna come, Kazakiri?
Please, Hyoka! I'd love
it if you'd join us!
Are you sure?
Of course! Let's go!
Well, okay.
Sounds like fun.
Oh... Well...
I should take out
some money first.
Oh, Himegami.
Didn't you notice that I just
transferred to your school...?
I didn't get a
very warm welcome.
Well, this is great...
I guess I'm one
of those girls
who's easy to overlook then.
Uh, no, not at all...
Oh, I know!
We were just about to
grab something to eat...
Wanna come with?
Perfect Komoe... Thank you.
-Huh?
-Nothing. Never mind...
I've got an errand to run,
so I can't hang out
with you now...
but I am curious.
Who is that?
Her name's Hyoka Kazakiri...
She's new.
Hyoka Kazakiri.
Are you sure that's her?
Pretty sure...
That's what she and
Index both say, anyway...
Do you know her?
Kirigaoka Girls' School.
It's the high school I went to
before that prep school...
I saw the name
Hyoka Kazakiri
while I was there, too.
If you went to
the same school,
does that mean she
has some rare ability,
like your Deep Blood?
I couldn't say.
Her name was always posted
at the top of the test rankings,
but no one had ever
actually seen her...
It was almost like she
was a ghost or something.
Nobody even knew what class
she was supposed to be in.
What's up with that?
I decided to check
out the anomaly...
That's how I found
her secret...
The girl named
Hyoka Kazakiri
is also known as
Counter Stop.
And that's not even the most
important thing I discovered.
Kazakiri is the key
to learning about
the Imaginary Number School
District's Five-Element Agency.
You mean it exists...?
The Five Element
Agency is real?
Word is they control
the administration
of Academy City
from the shadows.
It appears that she was
in a class by herself
designed to investigate
her own unique ability.
It's said to be part
of a lab set up to find
the true nature of the Imaginary
Number School District.
I don't understand why
she would be here though.
According to her,
she transferred in.
But I'm supposed to be
the only transfer student.
Be careful around her.
So this is the underground
world I've heard so much about.
-It's amazing!
-It's a mall.
An underground mall.
Well, Index, is there any
place in particular
you wanted to grab lunch...?
Anywhere too expensive or
with too long a line is out.
All that matters is
that the food is yummy.
It can be a cheapo
hole-in-the-wall for all I care!
Sounds good...
That okay with you?
You look frightened.
Was it something I said?
Oh... no...
It's not that I'm scared
of you or anything.
But you've seen me
practically naked.
Forget about it!
So, this student of
yours is having
a secret rendezvous with
a mysterious girl?
Man, I'm jealous of you.
My honor students would
never do something
as deliciously salacious.
Honestly...!I'm trying to tell
you about a possible threat,
and you're
laughing at me? !
This girl could
be the intruder.
What if she's
someone dangerous?
Are you prepared for that?
Oh, calm down...
Anyway, my current
information is that
there are actually two
intruders here in the city.
And that's what I'm trying
to verify right now.
How can we be certain...
there are only
two of them?
Yes, Yomikawa here...
I'll be right there.
Was that Antiskill
calling you in?
Looks like I've got some
serious work to do...
I'll have to
cut this short...
See ya later.
I brought the book you
asked me to locate for you.
Perfect... Good work, Himegami.
May I ask you something?
Yes?
Is there a student
enrolled in this school
who goes by the
name Hyoka Kazakiri?
I've got you now.
-An evacuation order!
-Run!
I'll have to ask you to remain
right where you are, please.
I'm Kuroko Shirai,
with Judgment,
the organization charged
with maintaining
the safety of Academy
City and its citizens.
I think you know why
you're being apprehended,
but I'd be happy to
explain if you need me to.
Search temporarily
suspended.
Get out of my
way, little girl.
Maybe I need to make your
situation a little clearer.
There we go...
Do you understand what
I'm saying better now?
What's happening? !
She's an outsider...!
How can she be an esper?
This isn't good... I need
to figure something out.
I don't know what all
this commotion is about.
But nobody messes with
a friend of mine
and gets away with it!
You should be
all right now.
Looks like that giant
mud guy was just a decoy.
So were you taking
her in for Judgment?
Yes, we were instructed
to apprehend her
for criminal trespassing.
You saved me...
You saved me, Sissy!
Ah, geez.
Good grief.
Hey...
Kuroko...
You know you can count
on me whenever, right?
I don't want you to think
you're putting me out
by asking for help.
Sissy, you really must
love me to hold me like this
and allow me
to burrow my face
deep into the valley
of your breasts!
Let go already, Kuroko!
This isn't what I
meant by helping you!
This most fundamental
and crucial knowledge
was widespread in the
days before Noah's Ark.
Even now, it is still
being disseminated
in fragments by
the chief Grigori,
though in a different manner.
In the beginning,
there was nothing
but the primordial earth...
Then God gave form
to the planet's dust,
breathed life into it,
and named it man.
In time, this sacred
process was revealed
to man by beings who
had fallen to the earth.
However, it was not a work
that could be undertaken
by the hands of mortals.
And so the life that
I brought forth
from the dust was only
a pale imitation.
A mere shadow of the being
I had sought to create.
The malformed
Golem Ellis...
Working tirelessly,
endlessly by my side.
Try not to keep me
waiting too long...
Ellis.
[Music]
The sorceress
Sherry Cromwell
calls forth the
monster Ellis...
We find ourselves
trapped underground,
caught up in a fierce battle.
Kazakiri, what
is your secret?
Next time, "Golem."
When science and magic cross
paths, a story is born.