I thought Misaka's
sister was dead...
Then suddenly more and more
versions of her appeared...
How many sisters
can one person have?
It turned out
that these clones
are part of a
military experiment.
There's something
very wrong happening
here in Academy City...
I need to find
that human bug zapper
and see how much she knows.
[Music]
So, you wanna know what
extra-sensory perception is?
I can explain best by
putting it in the context
of Schrödinger's theory.
I've never heard of him.
He was a professor
of quantum mechanics.
He's best known for the
Schrödinger's cat
thought experiment...
The premise itself
is a bit morbid,
so I'll alter it
for our purposes.
Now, as you can see, I'm
holding a box here in my hand.
Without opening it, guess
what's inside the box.
That's a silly question;
it's chocolate, of course...
It says right there it's
a box of chocolates.
No, sorry. You're wrong...
There are actually
hard candies inside.
No fair...!
That was a trick.
The meat is done.
Okay, Sister,
guess again...
What do you suppose is
hidden inside the box.
But you already
told me the answer.
You said it was
hard candies.
That's right...
but have you considered
the possibility
that I might be
lying to you?
So it's equally probable
that the box contains
chocolate or hard candy.
We won't know
unless we open it.
So, let's see...
It's not really chock
full of chocolate.
Pardon the pun.
All right, now
we do it again...
Tell me, Sister, what do
you suppose is inside the box?
You already showed me
there was chocolate inside.
Most people would answer
the same way as you:
they'd be 100% certain that
the box contains chocolate.
But what if there was
someone who believed
it was hard candy instead?
And what if
they opened the box
to find their
belief was reality?
Then that person would be
what we call an esper...
Such people can split
themselves off
from mainstream reality
and create a reality
that exists uniquely
for themselves.
How could they?
Why did everything have
to end up this way?
Excuse me.
Are you Mikoto Misaka?
It's very nice
to meet you.
You know what
paralysis is, right?
It's when a person has
lost the use of one
or more of their limbs.
Many people
suffer from this.
In a healthy body,
commands from the brain
are sent to the muscles
through electrical signals.
Paralysis is caused when
these signals cannot be sent,
but if we had the power
to control bioelectricity,
we might be
able to cure it.
By making use of your
particular ability,
we could help many
thousands of people.
Hey... did you hear?
There's a rumor
that they're making
military clones
in Academy City!
Yeah, and supposedly they're
using a Level 5's DNA map.
You don't think it's that
girl in our class, do ya?
Who needs you anyway!
Help us.
Somebody help us.
It's a cat.
Hey...
What do you think
you're doing...?
Answer me.
What's it to you? I can do
what I want when I want.
It's one of the privileges of
being the Level 5 Railgun...
Most people are smart
enough to stay clear
and not mess with me...
Any punk who
does is toast.
So maybe you should just
mind your own business
and leave me to mine.
Not gonna happen.
What's the big deal...?
Is your pride
still hurting
over the whole vending
machine episode yesterday?
You hoping to get me in
trouble for being out at night?
"An analysis of Tree
Diagram calculations
has been conducted."
"The optimal plan
would involve
creating 128
different battlefields
upon which Railgun
would be killed.
After that number
of victories,
Accelerator would then
advance to Level 6."
"Since that number of
Railguns cannot be produced,
a different plan
has been developed...
This plan will involve
the mass-production
of Railgun's
Level 5 "Sisters."
The numbers have
been adjusted."
"It has been
determined that
twenty thousand
different battlefields
and a corresponding
number of Sister deaths
will be needed to produce
the desired results."
Essentially that means...
Your younger
sisters were created
so they could be killed
as part of an experiment
to produce a Level 6.
Shame on you...
poking your nose in
where it
doesn't belong...
I had that file
securely hidden...
The fact that you're
holding it means
that you've been in my room
without my permission.
Normally I'd kill someone
for pulling a stunt like that.
Why are you here...?
Did you come because
reading the file
made you concerned
about me...?
Or just to tell me
you're disgusted?
Of course it made me
concerned about you.
You know, it's
surprisingly nice
to hear somebody say that,
even if it isn't the truth.
But it is the truth.
It's not.
I'm telling you,
I mean what I say!
I'm sorry for going in your
room without permission...
You can zap me as many
times as you want later,
I don't care...
Please, you have to tell
me what's going on here.
However you came
to have these plans,
I'm guessing it
wasn't legal.
Why are all those
laboratories marked like this?
Think about it for a sec.
They kind of look like
targets... don't they?
Because that's what
they are... Or were...
In the end
I decided against
using my Railgun
on all of them.
A high-tech
laboratory costs
hundreds of millions
to equip, right...?
If I wanted to,
I could use my powers
to short-circuit
everything.
It wouldn't be hard...
With the
equipment useless,
the lab would shut down...
and the project
would be stopped.
At least, that's what
was supposed to happen.
What happened instead?
It turns out...
it doesn't matter
how much I wreck,
the project is immediately
picked up by another lab.
All those scientists are
probably salivating
at the thought of being the ones
to create the first Level 6.
Know what they
call themselves...?
My sisters call themselves
laboratory rats,
and they really
believe it, too.
They know exactly
what's going on...
and what it
means for them.
But isn't human
cloning prohibited
under international law?
I think if you told
the governing board
what was happening...
Academy City is
under the watchful eye
of the Tree
Diagram satellite...
That means they have the
board's tacit approval.
At any rate, I'm the one who's
at the root of this problem...
They wouldn't be in this
if it weren't for me,
so I'm the one who
needs to save them.
It's pretty simple
when you think about it...
This experiment
is all about
building
Accelerator's ability.
The project revolves
around him,
so if he were
to disappear,
there would be no
reason for it to exist.
It'll never work.
You can't defeat Accelerator
in a fair fight, can you...?
From what I know
about you, if you could,
that would've been the
very first thing you tried.
Since he's still
around, that means
you know beating
him is impossible.
You might be close,
but you're no match for
Accelerator, are you?
Why didn't you just
ask somebody for help...?
Once you knew you
couldn't do it yourself,
why not reach out
and ask someone to
help you take him down?
Why did they create
twenty-thousand Sisters?
Because they weren't able
to create 128 Railguns.
And what did they need 128
Railguns for in the first place?
Because by killing
Railgun 128 times,
Accelerator would
advance to Level 6.
What if...
What if I wasn't actually
worth as much as they think?
Accelerator is
supposed to develop
from repeated experience
in hard combat...
What if the project
leaders could be convinced
that wouldn't happen?
You know, they actually
used Tree Diagram
to determine exactly how a
fight between Accelerator
and me would play out.
The computer calculated that
I would die after 185 moves.
But, you see... if I was
to be unceremoniously beaten
after the very
first move...
Well, faced
with that data,
surely the researchers
would have to conclude
that something was wrong with
the original programming.
Yeah... but even if
you fooled them once,
wouldn't they just
do some recalculations
and start things
back up again?
They wouldn't
be able to...
That's what makes
this plan so perfect.
The Tree Diagram satellite
was actually attacked
from the ground and brought
down a few weeks back...
The source of the attack
hasn't been determined.
There could be no
recalculations...
Regardless of how much
data they have,
without the computer
to analyze it,
they'd have no choice
but to stop the project.
So that's it...
I get it.
Basically, you
want to die.
Yeah.
You believe that by
sacrificing yourself,
you can save the ten thousand
Sisters who remain...
Is that right?
That's the plan.
I'm actually on my way to
see Accelerator right now...
and once I'm done...
This whole twisted experiment
will come to an end.
Stand aside.
I'm not moving.
You idiot! Don't you realize
what's on the line, here? !
If I don't do this,
then ten thousand of my
Sisters are going to be killed!
Or are you so
heartless you think
since they're just
a bunch of clones,
it's no big deal
if they die? !
Not at all.
I think their deaths
would be a tragedy...
but I also think there must
be some other way to stop it.
I'm not gonna
let you do this.
So... You really mean to
stand in my way...
You're choosing
my single life
over the lives of ten
thousand of my Sisters.
Don't you get it...? I
can't bear to stand by
and do nothing
while they die.
I'm going to save
them by myself.
This is the last
warning I'll give you...
Get out of my way!
I'm still not sure
what kind of power
you used against me before.
But I do know I can't
afford to lose to you today!
So you'd better
be ready to fight
like your life
depends on it.
Otherwise...
You'll be the
one who dies.
What're you doing...?
Why are you standing
there like that?
You're seriously going to
try to stop me, aren't you?
All right, then...
You should know I'm
not going to hold back.
I'm going to get by you
one way or another...
Even if I have
to shoot you!
I won't fight you.
Whatever you do... I won't.
Then just stand aside...
Let me do this...
Why can't you see there are no
other options left to me...?
This isn't some petty problem
that will just go away.
It's evil like you've
never seen before...
It's the slaughter of ten
thousand innocent people!
Passive resistance
isn't the solution
to a problem like this!
It doesn't matter.
Do what you want, but
I won't fight you.
I'm telling you right
now, you will fight me.
Like it or not...
You will fight me!
Last chance...
I won't miss with
the next one.
If you wanna stop me, step
up and fight like a man...
and if you won't, then get
the hell out of my way!
Don't pretend to understand
the situation I'm in.
Someone like you
could never get it!
Oh, no.
Why? Why?
I don't get it...
Why won't you fight me?
I don't... know why.
I don't really
think I can give you
a clear reason for it...
It's just how I feel...
I don't know what to do...
and I don't know if there
are any other solutions.
But I do know...
I don't want this.
I don't want to see
you get hurt Mikoto...
I can't let you do it.
It's not right...
It's not right that
you should have to die.
No one should...
Why does anyone
have to die tonight?
I can't believe that
that's the only way!
Help me.
Somebody help me.
Just shut up, you fool.
Stop babbling comforting
words trying to reassure me.
I promise I don't
deserve it, not anymore.
Maybe the world you live in
is full of happy endings...
Maybe good always
triumphs over evil.
Not for me...
There's no place for me
in a world like that.
Why can't you
see the truth?
Your death isn't
the answer....
It won't help
anyone in the end.
Say you die...
and your Sisters
survive...
Say your sacrifice
actually does save them
from being killed
by Accelerator.
Do you think they'll be
grateful for what you did...?
Do you think they
want to be saved
at the expense
of your life? !
Just shut up!
Don't talk about things
you can't understand...
Do you think I'm
some kind of saint?
Because I can
assure you I'm not.
Why don't you get it...?
You know full well
I'm responsible
for the deaths of thousands.
I deserve to
be punished...
There's no place for a monster
like me in this world...
Not anymore.
Why are you even
doing this...?
Why are you
risking your life
to stick up for a
monster like me? !
You're not a monster.
If you were, I wouldn't
still be alive.
There's no way I should
still be standing here
after taking a direct
body hit like that.
You must've been
subconsciously holding back.
Holding back?
No way. I gave
it all I had...
I meant it when I said I
was going to kill you...
I knew you weren't going
to make any moves
to fight back at me...
-but even so
-Admit the truth...
You couldn't bring
yourself to kill me.
You just couldn't do it...
Saving your Sisters is the
most important thing to you...
and maybe you hate me for
standing in your way like this.
But here I am...
Ultimately, you're
a good enough person
that you couldn't
kill me...
even though I stood
between you and your goal.
I'm trying to do
something good here...
by sacrificing myself
so they won't die.
That should be enough
reason to do it!
You're making way
this too complicated.
I die they live. It's simple!
And more than that,
it's the right thing to do!
Step aside and let me
do what I know is right!
I won't.
Then you'll die.
There's no way you'll
survive this next attack...
Not if you stand there
and take it head-on.
Now move...
Unless you want this
to be your death!
I won't move.
Don't get up.
No... Please stop.
Please don't...
I can't do this.
[Music]
She told me...
she has no choice
but to die.
She doesn't want to die...
She shouldn't
have to die...
But she says she
has no choice.
There has to be
some other option.
Just think... there
has to be a way...
There must be
something else...
All those scientists are
probably salivating
at the thought of being the ones
to create the first Level 6.
To stop the experiment,
we have to make them think
that their original
premise was incorrect...
With the computer gone,
they'll have no choice
but to abandon the project.
Maybe...
One of Misaka's Sisters
is headed for
the testing grounds,
where the strongest Level
5 in Academy City waits...
What will become of
her when they meet?
Next time, "Accelerator."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.