It turns out that Index's
photographic memory
is not actually a condition
that could lead to her death
without annual
memory erasure...
Does this mean the church has
been lying to Stiyl and Kanzaki?
Locating most
effective magic...
Desired combination
for intruder repulsion
has been successfully
acquired.
Now deploying
specified magic...
Employing Saint George's
Holy Sanctuary...
The intruder
will be destroyed.
[Music]
There's something I've
thought didn't quite fit
since all of this
first started.
You're not an esper
like the students here.
Yet you told me you
weren't able to use magic.
That's impossible!
She told you the truth...
She can't use magic.
Don't you see
what's happening?!
The church has been lying
to you this entire time
about Index having
no magical ability.
Yeah, do you get it now...?
And that thing
about her dying
if her memory's
not erased every year,
that's another whopper.
The only thing
killing her right now
is whatever magic the
church planted in her.
We just have to find
a way to stop it...
After that's done, there won't
be any need to erase her memory.
Think about it this way...
The church made Index
memorize a bunch of evil books
without a second thought about
her safety or happiness.
That's the kind of
group they are...
Do you think they'd
be likely to share
their true plans
with low-level enforcers?
Not convinced...?
Why don't you ask Index
about it yourselves?
Saint George's Holy Sanctuary
is having no effect on
the intruder's opposition...
Now switching to a
more effective spell...
Attempt to destroy the
intruder will continue.
Fortis Nine-Three-One!
I'm not interested in hearing
your unproven theories...
What we know for
certain is this...
If we do this, then we
save her for the time being.
I'll do whatever it takes to
make sure that happens...
I'll kill you if I must...
That's what I decided...
long ago...
So give up.
"For the time being"?
That's not much
of a promise...
I'm talking about
saving her for good...
There's only one question you
need to ask yourself, sorcerer.
Do you want to help Index,
or are you too afraid to?
You guys have been
waiting for a long time...
You want a happy ending
for all this, don't you...?
One in which you don't have
to be Index's enemy...
You wanna be her
friends in truth
and not the people who
snatch her memories away
from her every year.
You never gave up
hope completely...
You never stopped trying...
Because you made a promise
to yourself not to abandon her.
Knowing what you
would have to do,
you made it your personal
mission to save this girl
who had been your friend
and companion.
You wanted to be the
heroes of this story...
So why content yourselves
with supporting roles now...?
You told me earlier you swore to
protect her with your lives,
no matter who or
what got in the way.
If so, your part
is far from over.
It's barely even begun.
Are you gonna give up
because Act One turned out
to be a little
on the long side?
If you help me instead
of fighting me...
then maybe you'll get
your happy ending...
Now let's do this!
Salvare Zero-Zero-Zero!
What are those... lights?
I know this...
It's Dragon's Breath...
Its power is equal to the
legendary dragon strike
of St. George.
If even one of those
touches you....
you're in big trouble.
Innocentius!
You're up...!
Move it, esper!
Urgent Warning.
Reading from
Chapter 6, Verse 13...
New opponent has
been identified....
Altering combat strategy.
Beginning a survey
of the battle scene...
Completed...
Prioritizing the
destruction of intruders.
Strongest threat, Toma Kamijo,
will be destroyed first.
Urgent Warning.
From Chapter 22...
begin Verse 1...
Successfully recalculated
for flame magic.
A distorted version of the
church of the cross spell
has been detected,
along with multiple runes.
Formulating counter-church
of the cross spell.
Saint George's
Holy Sanctuary...
activating stage two...
Eli, eli, lama,
sabachthani.
She's countering my flames!
God, they say you
are good and just...
If that's true,
then I will be able to
destroy this evil magic.
Are you good?
Will you do justice?
We'll find out right now!
Warning...
Last... Chapter...
Verse...
Zero.
Collar... has sustained...
critical... damage.
John's Pen ...
failing.
How odd...
Apparently, a
mysterious blast of light
tore through one of our
observation satellites.
Umm... You and your
two other companions...
It seems that all three
of you were in Academy City
without any form
of identification...
would you happen
to know anything
about this strange event?
No.
All right...
and that letter there...
It was sent by one of the
other foreigners, was it?
Whoa-whoa-whoa...!
I don't think it
was meant for you...
It was clearly
addressed to the boy;
it's for him to open.
He won't mind.
"Any salutation would sound
phony, so I'll just skip it."
You did a damn fine
job back there, esper...
I could probably say more,
but what's the point...?
Writing down what I felt
and what went through
my mind that night
would require a whole
rainforest worth of paper...
So I'll skip that, too.
Instead, as a token of my
gratitude for your help,
I'll tell you more
about our mutual friend
and the peculiar situation
she's found herself in.
The church wanted us to
bring her back immediately...
However, they
changed their minds
when we asked about those
lies you uncovered...
After that, they
told us to simply
"maintain the current status."
Which basically translates as
"wait and see what happens."...
Personally, I don't much
like the idea of her
being with you for a moment
longer than necessary.
I'm sure it will come as
no particular surprise
that I'm not
planning to give up
and turn her over
to you indefinitely.
We will be gathering
the necessary data,
and once we have all the
information we require,
we intend to come
back and reclaim her.
But you need not
fear another attack.
"For now, just wait
until I contact you again."
That's quite a mischievous
friend you've got there...
the letter must've
been dipped
in a liquid explosive
of some kind.
I know you're anxious
from waiting ...
You're eager to
see for yourself
how the boy is holding up...
It might do him good
to have a visitor.
Still... if you seem
shocked by his condition,
it might frighten him...
So let me give you some
tips before going in.
May I have your
attention please...
We would like to remind
all friends and family
that visiting hours
will end at 9 p.m...
If you would like to remain at
the hospital later than this,
please see the information
desk for approval...
-Yes?
-The gift shop and the cafeteria
will remain open until 8 p.m.
Hi, Toma.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry...
but I think you might be
looking for a different room.
His memories haven't
just been lost...
They've been
completely obliterated.
What do you mean?
What's the difference?
It's not a normal
case of memory loss...
The brain cells that
managed his memories
have been physically
destroyed.
I'd be very surprised
if he remembered
anything from his past.
What happened to him...?
It's like his skull
was cracked open,
and his brain was
hit with a stun gun.
Um... Are you feeling
all right, miss...?
You look awfully pale...
Like you've had
a terrible shock.
Oh no, I'm fine.
Really. I'm just
fine, thank you.
Ya know...
you look familiar...
Have we maybe met before?
Of course...
don't you remember...?
We have met...
It was out on the balcony
of your student dormitory.
I see...
I lived in a student dorm
before this happened.
That's right...
I showed up one day...
You gave me some food....
and you used your right hand
to destroy my Walking Church.
Did you say
"Walking Church"?
What's that...?
And why would I
destroy one of them?
Come on...
You have to remember...
Think, Toma...
How could you forget
fighting those two sorcerers
who had been chasing me?
You called me Toma...
Whose name is that?
It was yours...
but you don't remember.
My name is Index...
and I want you to know...
even though you don't
remember it, I loved you.
I'm sorry.
Index is a funny name...
It doesn't sound like something
a girl would be called...
Maybe... you're talking
about a pet I had?
Hah-hah! Gotcha!
Hook, line, and sinker!
Toma?
What, did I hurt
your feelings
by comparing you
to an animal?
Be a little adventurous...
We could get you
a nice collar...
Come on, it'll be fun...
Would you rather
be a dog or a cat?
I'm guessing cat ...
I, uh...
I'm confused...
I thought your brain cells
had been destroyed...
and your memory
was gone completely.
Hey, now... you almost
make it sound like
you wish I had
forgotten everything...
Well?
No... I don't...
So, according to the
doctor with the frog face...
my memory cells have been
utterly obliterated...
and because of that,
I should've forgotten everything
that's ever happened to me.
What do you mean...
you should have?
Well, here's the thing...
All that supposed damage was
inflicted by a magic spell...
That alone explains it
all, doesn't it...?
When I touched you on the head,
it was with my right hand...
That's all I needed to do.
Imagine Breaker took care
of the rest, no problem.
Imagine... Breaker?
Yeah, my right hand...
That's what the doctor
called it, anyway...
It neutralized the power
of the magic spell...
and since it never had the
chance to reach my brain,
I came out all right.
Man, the look on your
face was priceless...!
I mean, you're usually the one
going around saying crazy stuff
and messing with
people's heads.
I have to admit,
it was pretty fun
to turn the tables
on you this time.
Uh...
Uh oh...
You should see a doctor.
I'm dead...
She's gonna kill me.
Listen, son...
are you sure about
what you're doing?
You... you don't remember
anything, do you?
I told you what
happened...
every last detail
that those other two
gave me about the event.
No, I don't...
but for some reason
I can't explain...
the last thing in
the world I wanted was
to see that girl cry...
It must sound really
strange to you.
I'm not really sure what
this feeling is exactly...
but it's there...
even if I never
remember the reason why.
And that's okay...
because I don't
wanna let it go.
So...
I guess one memory was
left to me after all, huh?
Your memories are dead.
They were destroyed
with your brain cells...
All past information was
blasted irreversibly
out of your brain.
So then ...
Where do you think
this remembered feeling
is coming from?
Where is it stored?
Well, doctor...
That should be obvious.
From my heart...
wouldn't you agree?
Two weeks have now passed
since a mysterious incident
caused us to lose contact
with our satellite Orihime I.
So far, all efforts to
reestablish contact have failed.
The governing board has
convened an emergency session
to hear further suggestions
from Academy City scientists.
Stiyl Magnus...
You are no different
from the others.
Every person
who comes here
has the same reaction to my
rather unusual appearance.
But it makes sense to me...
If machines can
sustain my life,
why make my body do it.
Yes...
Director-General Aleister.
I believe you are already
aware of the reason
you have been called
back here from England.
A situation has developed.
If you mean Deep Blood,...
I know.
We have indeed
located a young girl
who possesses the ability
to kill a certain creature...
a creature that we aren't
even sure actually exists.
Here is where it
gets complicated...
Sorcerers aren't usually
allowed in the city...
and yet one has involved
himself in this.
In Academy City?
Crushing a sorcerer
is no problem...
If pressed we
could handle it ...
but of course, I would prefer
to avoid such a conflict...
Pitting members
of the scientific
and magical disciplines
against each other
is a dangerous game...
as you know.
Scientists and magicians...
each side with its own power,
its own exclusive knowledge...
The harmony of this division
keeps the world in balance.
Academy City is
bursting with espers...
Suppose a sorcerer
was brought down
by someone with
psychic talent...
You can imagine the disquiet
that would cause... can't you?
I can, sir.
But you believe that the
problem can be solved
by sending a fellow member
of the magical community
to deal with this sorcerer?
That is my plan...
Additionally,
I have at my disposal
one of the natural
enemies of sorcery.
Do you mean...
Imagine Breaker?
But sir...
I thought the idea was to
avoid using espers at all.
That won't be an issue...
He's a Level Zero, with
no abilities to speak of.
He has no access to
privileged information...
So using him will not
risk a security breach...
Yet he will be helpful
in dealing with our
sorcerer friend.
Basically... you
brought me back here...
to team up with the boy.
He does not have the brains
to understand your magic...
nor does he possess the
power to recreate it.
You won't have to worry about
your magical secrets
being revealed.
I will do as you wish.
But, sir...
We've never seen the
power of Deep Blood...
Can we even be certain
it truly exists...?
And if we learn
that it does,
think of the ramifications...
It would prove...
It would prove the existence
of dangerous creatures
that would need to be
hunted down and killed.
You speak of vampires.
That is more of a
question for your side.
I believe the occult is
your domain, not ours.
You know...
It seems we are presented
with an interesting
philosophical question...
if the existence of
Deep Blood proves
the existence of vampires...
what exactly does the
Imagine Breaker prove?
[Music]
The alchemist Aureolus Izzard
is holding something
called Deep Blood...
This power is being kept
in a school, and it is...
What...? It's a girl?
Next time,
"The Science Cult."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.