Index's perfect memory
comes with a drawback...
85% of her brain is
taken up by the grimoires,
which leaves only 15%
for other functions...
The sorcerers say
that because of this,
they have to erase her memory
every year or she will die...
Only three days remain until
they perform the ceremony.
Wait... there were
three days...
I've been asleep how long?
[Music]
Okay, Kamijo, I'm
heading out now...
I won't be back until late,
so you're in charge...
Be a good boy and
keep an eye on things here
for me, all right?
But I ask one thing:
I don't want you
hurting Toma anymore!
The limit will be
reached in twelve hours
and thirty-eight minutes.
We wanted to see
if the ball and chain
was sufficient to keep you
from running away again...
It worked better
than we thought.
The ball and chain?
You don't want your little
toy taken away, do you...?
If not, you'd best abandon
any thoughts of running...
Understood?
It'll be all right.
I can work out a
deal with them...
and your life can go back to
how it was before you met me.
I promise...
I'm not going to let them
bother you anymore...
I...
Index, what happened?
I'll make this quick.
Hello...? Can you hear me?
Yeah... Kanzaki, wasn't it?
It doesn't matter....
There's no need for
pleasantries now......
is Index there with you?
I'd rather not
wake her up.
No, that's perfect...
Just listen to
what I have to say.
It's almost time...
She'll reach her limit
tonight at midnight.
At that exact hour,
we'll begin the ceremony
to erase her memories...
The one that will
save her life.
Why would you go out of your
way to tell me your plans?
Knowing what to expect is
only gonna make it
that much easier
for me to fight you.
Don't you want the opportunity
to say goodbye to her?
This is not a matter
open for debate
or negotiation...
This is an order...
You will say your farewells
before we arrive...
And then you will
leave that place.
Do you understand me?
You people are
unbelievable...
Index is paying the price
for your incompetence...
I thought you
guys knew sorcery.
Can't you do anything with
your magic to help her? !
She's got a hundred and three
thousand books in her head!
Maybe one of those
has the answer!
The church
can't allow that.
Index turning on them
is their greatest fear.
What are you
talking about?
The grimoires are full of
dangerous information...
The church decreed that
Index would not be allowed
access to anything in them
that dealt with
memory manipulation.
Fine... then why not try to get
to them with your own magic?
The church is also very
concerned about sorcerers
outside of Necessarius
gaining access to the books.
Take my word for it;
the grimoires are
very well protected.
And then, of course,
there's the fact
that the act of reading the
grimoires defiles the mind.
You knew that... and you still
let Index memorize them? !
We weren't told until
it was already done...
Our magic cannot help her.
Trust me.
All right then...
but what about us?
What do you mean?
I'm talking
about science...
I bet there are any
number of ways to erase
someone's memory
by using science.
You've said magic can't be
used to get to those books,
but maybe there's
something else that can...
This is Academy
City, remember...
There are plenty
of espers here
who know about
manipulating the mind...
I say it's still too
soon to abandon all hope.
But maybe you'd rather
go for the quick fix
you know will work instead
of taking on a challenge...
Never mind that it's
your supposed friend's
happiness we're
talking about here.
Talk is cheap...
Results are what
we're interested in.
And, to use your words,
we do indeed know
that our "quick fix"
will have the desired
result of saving her life.
We can't be certain
something else would work
so any other method
would be a gamble....
It isn't a matter of not
wanting to take on a challenge.
We don't want to be reckless
with somebody else's life.
In that case...
I don't think we'll ever
see eye-to-eye on this...
No surprise there.
But you should know...
I'm still gonna
fight you...
no matter what!
You should stay
out of my way...
I don't care what I do to
you if it means saving her.
If anything happens to her
while she's in your care,
you can consider
your life forfeit...
I will see you at
midnight tonight...
You only have a short
time remaining now.
If you want to spend it
fighting a losing battle,
it's up to you.
Let's see...
"Memory loss is commonly
caused by old age
or over consumption
of alcohol ...
It may also occur
following an interruption
of blood flow to
the brain."
"Drug induced:
Certain medicines may
also cause memory loss...
Among these are general
anesthetics such as
halothane as well as
some benzodiazepines."
Forget it. This isn't
getting me anywhere.
What is that?
Miss Komoe's cell
phone statement.
That might work!
I'll ask Miss Komoe if
she knows the number
to any research lab that
might deal with neurology.
Oh, come on...
Pick up the phone!
I guess all I can do now
is call up some places
at random and hope. "...
Next up.
Damn it!
Hi... is someone there?
Research on
photographic memory?
Yes... I'm familiar with it.
What's the problem?
Can you describe the
issue in detail for me?
Magic...? Seriously?
What do you think
you're doing
making a prank call
at this hour?
It's nearly midnight.
Hello...?.. Are
you still there?
Hello...?
Oh, for crying out loud!
We've run out of time.
Move it.
We'll refer to the
Book of Crowley...
We need to call
down an angel...
and raise a temple
in this room.
We need to root out
every last memory.
Wait... just hold on...
Think about it!
There are over
1.8 million espers
here in Academy City...
and more than a
thousand research labs.
If we check out
those possibilities,
we might not have to resort
to something so drastic.
You guys don't want this to
happen to her either, right...?
Deep down you're
hoping and praying
that there's some other
way, aren't you?
So it's simple ...
just wait a
little longer...
I promise... I'll
find another way...
Whatever it takes,
I'll find something that
works for everybody.
Are you done talking,
or is there more?
Look! If she wasn't
unconscious now,
would you be saying
the same thing...?
She's endured this
hell for so long...
She's in so much pain she
can't open her eyes,
and you'd tell
her: "Sit tight,
there's something
I wanna try."
You'd have doctors
you never met before
poking around in her body,
pumping her full of drugs...
all on the off chance
that maybe it'll work? !
What kind of a
person are you?
Answer me...!
Are you truly
a human being,
or a monster who's
wearing human skin?
Do you see this...?
It's a magical artifact
necessary for erasing
her memories.
All you have to do is touch
it with your right hand,
and it will lose
all its power.
The only thing that
we'll be taking from Index
is her memory...
a small price to pay...
but you...
if whatever you want
to attempt fails,
you'll be taking
away her life.
Knowing that...
do you still wanna try?
Can you sit here, watching
her struggle bravely,
and decide to risk her life?
If you're so sure
it's going to work,
why do you hesitate...?
Go ahead and
play the hero!
I'm Index. Nice
to meet you!
Do you have
any food in there?
I'm really starving...
Please feed me!
The ceremony will
commence at 12:15 a.m.
We'll use the power of Leo
to perform the memory erasure.
All right.
Hey... sorcerer guy...
What am I supposed
to say to her
when I... when I
tell her goodbye?
If you hadn't
noticed, I'm busy.
I don't have time
to give you advice...
What you need to do
right now is shut up...
and get out of here.
Your right hand
extinguished my flames...
I still can't comprehend
the principles at work there,
but I don't want it
to have any influence
on the ceremony
we're about to perform,
no matter how
minor it may be.
Useless...
I'm useless...
What good am I if I can't
even save this one girl
from suffering
such a huge loss?
There is still
enough time left...
We have ten minutes
before we need to begin.
Do you remember what
it was like for us
the first time we had to
erase her memories?
We spent the whole night
by her side, sobbing.
No... no way...
Who knows what that kid
might try to pull
if we leave him here?
If we take our eyes off
him for a second,
he could do something
that kills them both!
If that were really true,
wouldn't he have touched
the cross when you gave
him the opportunity?
You only gave
him that test
because you knew
he would pass...
You knew he wouldn't
risk her life.
Yeah, maybe...
Either way, we cannot
perform the ceremony
until the time is right...
It's riskier to deny
him his goodbye...
Without that closure, he
might change his mind
and interrupt us at a
crucial moment...
Just let him.
Just ten minutes... Understood?
To... ma...?
Index...
I'm sorry.
Toma...
Some kind of array has
been set up in the room.
They said it was
recovery magic.
Recovery magic?
Who said that?
Those sorcerers
came back, didn't they?
Go now! You have
to get out of here!
No... it's fine...
I'm staying.
-Toma!
-It's all done...
It's over.
For now, at
least, it's over.
Toma...
I'm sorry...
I'll get stronger, and this
will never happen again...
I'll punish every
single person
who is responsible for
doing this to you...
When I'm done with them,
they'll regret this
more than anything else
they've ever done
in their lives.
Just you wait...
Next time, I swear
I'll save you...
Next time I
will not fail...
no matter what
I have to do.
Thank you, Toma...
I'll be waiting.
Damn it.
Is this really the
way it has to end?
It's not fair...
There must've been something
else I could've done...
Something to get to
those damn books
that are taking up 85%
of Index's brain.
Something to save the memories
she does have left...
She should get to control more
than a sliver of her own brain.
Wait...
A full 85% of Index's
brain is used to store
the hundred and three
thousand grimoires...
As a result, she has only
15% of her brain remaining
to control
day-to-day functions.
Index's memory
erasure is conducted
at precise yearly
intervals.
Hang on a second...
How is it that only a
year's worth of memories
can fit into that
leftover fifteen percent?
And another thing...
how did they arrive at those
figures in the first place...?
They seem like
arbitrary percentages,
not precise calculations.
Yes? Oh, hi Kamijo.
I recognized your voice.
What are you doing
using my phone
without asking
permission first?
Huh? ... What's that about
photographic memory...?
Yeah... it exists...
It's a rare ability that
very few people have...
Was there something specific
you want to know about it?
Someone told me a year's
worth of memories
take up fifteen percent of
a person's brain capacity...
but if that's true...
what about people who have
photographic memories...?
Wouldn't their brains
become overloaded
around the time
they're seven years old?
It's true that somebody
with a photographic memory
is unable to
forget anything.
The memories are permanent,
no matter how
trivial they are...
but even so it's impossible
for someone's memories
to overload their brain.
In fact, some studies
indicate that the human brain
is able to store up to
a hundred and forty
years of memories.
It's impossible for memories
to overload the human brain?
Human memory is
really complex.
There's more than
one kind, you know.
There's semantic memory,
which handles language
and knowledge...
Procedural memory, which
handles motor skills
that are acquired
over time...
and episodic memory, which
handles memories of past events.
Kinda nifty the way it's
all split up like that, huh?
Oh, yeah. Very nifty...
So, Miss Komoe, what
exactly are you telling me?
I'll sum it up for you...
It doesn't matter how much
knowledge you acquire...
Neurologically speaking,
there is absolutely no way
that your memories could
make your brain explode
or anything close to it.
According to what
Miss Komoe says
Index's photographic memory
isn't actually a
life-threatening condition.
If that's the case...
it has to mean the church
is lying to Kanzaki.
But there's no question
that Index is suffering.
The church must have tampered
with her brain somehow...
They rigged it
so if her memories
aren't erased on a
yearly basis, she'll die.
They need to
ensure that Index,
the keeper of the
grimoire library,
will never turn
against them.
And Index's friends, too.
The church needs
to make sure
they'll do what
they're told.
All right...
So what exactly did they
do to make her this way?
If you're so sure
it's going to work,
why do you hesitate...?
Go ahead
and play the hero!
I won't play the hero.
I will be the hero!
Okay...
let's see...
There doesn't seem to
be any change yet...
so I haven't come in
contact with any magic...
All right, maybe...
they put it someplace
I haven't touched yet?
No, they wouldn't...
Urgent Warning...
Read from
Chapter 3, Verse 2.
A rupture has been
detected in all barriers,
from one through three.
Regeneration
provisions failing...
Auto-regeneration
not possible.
Action required to
preserve the library.
Assigning priority to
interception of the intruder.
Currently reverse-calculating
the magic formula
that has penetrated the barriers
by accessing the library.
Failure... Unable to
locate relevant magic.
Breaking down formula
composition to develop
a local weapon that
will counter the intruder.
Locating most
effective magic...
Desired combination
for intruder repulsion
has been successfully
acquired.
Now deploying
specified magic...
Employing Saint George's
Holy Sanctuary...
The intruder
will be destroyed.
[Music]
Saint George's
Holy Sanctuary creates
a seemingly endless distance
between Index and me...
but I'm just
one step away...
One more step and
I know I'll reach her!
Next time,
"Imagine Breaker."
When science and
magic cross paths...
a story is born.