[Music]
That's my rotten
luck for you!
Get back here,
you scrawny punk!
Running won't
save you kid!
My name is Toma Kamijo...
And this little chase scene
is just another event
in an adolescence riddled
with nothing but
rotten luck.
[Music]
It was July 19th...
I entered the restaurant,
excited that summer break
was beginning the next day...
I intended to order
myself a nice big meal
to celebrate the start
of the vacation...
but that's when I saw it.
I could tell that sleazebag
was up to no good...
I had to step in and
help the poor girl...
What else could
I do, really?
Well, honey...?
Let's go.
Excuse me...
You should go...
You're bothering
the young lady.
-I'm starving.
-Tell me about it.
Want something, kid?
A beating, maybe...?
Well?
Man, what was I thinking...?
With my luck, I should've
known this would happen!
Finally...! They got
tired of running.
What was all that about?
Playing the hero by protecting
some dimwitted thugs...?
What, are you a
teacher or something?
So they only stopped
running after me because...
You got it...
They were starting
to annoy me,
so I dealt with them.
Yeah, it figures.
Hey, hero...
you ever heard of...
a railgun?
Railgun...? Um...
A super-electromagnetic
gun...
It's an application of Fleming's
kinetic momentum theory...
You use it to
launch projectiles
with a little extra oomph.
Allow me to demonstrate
it for you...
Catch!
When it's launched at three
times the speed of sound...
Even something small
packs a big punch.
Is that what you used to
take care of those guys?
Don't be such a moron.
There are easier ways
to take care of a bunch
of level zeroes...
And I know them all.
Yep. As it turned out,
it wasn't her
that needed saving...
It was those poor saps
who were careless enough
to get on her bad side.
So, you're one of the seven
Level 5 espers in Academy City.
Tell me, are the
other six this rude,
or are you just special?
You could stand to be
less condescending...
Humility's a
virtue you know.
Y' must be good...
or you wouldn't
talk to me that way.
Wa-wa-wa-wait...!
I'm just a Level Zero.
So... If you're really a
Level Zero like you say...
Explain how you don't
have a scratch on you.
I don't know
what to tell you.
Maybe it's coincidence...
or just plain bad luck.
Either way...
this really
isn't your night.
Last night's lightning
caused a power outage...
which turned my place into
a sweltering cesspool.
Hot...
It also meant that
everything in my refrigerator
had become toxic.
On top of that, I lost
my emergency rations
when they fell
in the sink...
I crushed my cash card
when I was looking
for my wallet...
And then someone
called to inform me
that I'm such an idiot,
I need to take
a remedial class.
Just my luck.
All right, it's a
nice day outside...
Maybe airing the mattress
out will improve my mood.
Yep, my future might
be dark and gloomy...
but at least it's a
beautiful, sunny day!
Then again...
now that I said that, it'll
probably start pouring rain.
Huh?
I already hung
something...?
That's strange...
That's... a girl...
What's she doing
on my balcony?
That clothing...
she looks like a Sister!
I'm guessing she's not
from around here....
I'm so...
I'm so very... hungry.
Very, very hungry.
What was that?
I said I'm hungry.
What... the...
Are you listening to me?
I told you, I'm hungry.
So, uh...
just out of curiosity...
Is this something
you make a habit of?
Randomly appearing draped
over people's balconies?
It's also called
curb-croaking.
So... Do you have
any food in there?
I'm really starving...
Please feed me!
I think she'd be
better off some place
far, far away from here.
Do you think this'll
do the trick?
Yes, thank you...!
Sandwiches are my favorite!
Wonderful...! This
tastes fantastic!
Oh... Really, it does?
That's a surprise,
considering it's a stir-fry
made of spoiled ingredients
from a dead refrigerator.
I know what it is...!
There's some
sour flavor in here
that's really
waking up my taste buds.
What a great idea!
It's sour?
Don't feel like you
have to eat it all...
It's bachelor
cooking--nothing exciting.
You don't need
to be so modest...
It was very kind of you
to go to the trouble
of making it
for me at all...
So I'm going to finish
every last morsel!
I give!
I can't do it!
So, uh... Do you
mind telling me
why you were hanging
out on my balcony?
Oh, I fell...
What I was actually
trying to do
was jump from one roof
onto the next over.
Huh...? But this building
is eight stories high!
I didn't exactly
have many options...
I was being pursued...
Whoops, I never
introduced myself, did I?
Well, how rude of me...!
I'm Index. Nice to meet you!
Index? That's your name?
That sounds like
an alias to me...
You can't tell me you're
named after part of a book.
Yes the Index Librorum
Prohibitorum...
Oh... and my magic name is
Dedicatus Five-Four-Five...
It translates as
"the consecrated lamb
who safeguards the
wisdom of the mighty."
Okay, Index, why exactly
would somebody be chasing
a Sister like you?
I believe they seek
the one hundred and
three thousand grimoires
that I carry with me.
Grim... wha?
Well...
The Book of Eibon...
The Lemegeton...
The Book of the Dead...
Those are a just few typical
examples of grimoires.
So where are they...?
It's hard to believe
you're hiding a whole
library under that dress.
I'm carrying all one hundred
and three thousand volumes!
That's more books than
I've even seen before...
What...? Y'mean you got a key
to a warehouse or something?
Mm-mm.
Is this some
kind of joke...?
Next, are you gonna say,
"Well, stupid people
can't see them."
It isn't just stupid
people who can't...
The whole point is for
them not to be visible.
Okay, so who is it
that's chasing you?
A sorcery society.
Huh...? Sorcery?
Surely you've heard
of sorcerers before...
People who do magic...
a magic cabal.
Uh, do you belong
to one of those
new-age religions
or something?
Wait, are you
making fun of me?
You are, aren't you?
You're making fun of me!
I'm sorry.
It's too much.
I know there are plenty
of unusual powers
being used out
in the world.
but I just can't buy magic.
This is Academy City...
Supernatural abilities
aren't really anything new
and different here...
Anybody can develop them if
they use science, not magic.
You believe in supernatural,
psychic powers,
but the idea of sorcery
is "too much" for you?
Well, okay...
Explain what
sorcery is, then...
Or maybe show
me an example.
I can't do that. I don't
possess any magical power.
If you can't use it,
then how are you so convinced
that it actually exists?
Because it does!
Sorcery does exist!
To tell you the truth
I was born
with a kind of strange,
inexplicable power myself.
What kind of power?
It's something in
my right hand...
When it comes in contact
with any unusual ability,
my hand cancels it out.
Who knows? It may even
work on divine miracles.
Well?
What's with the face?
You look like you're listening
to a used car salesman.
Can you blame me?
I'm guessing you probably
don't even believe in God...
and you're telling me your
super-special right hand
has the power to
cancel a miracle!
What a joke...
You still like to
play make-believe,
and you're the one
making fun of me?!
Magic's not make-believe!
Then why not show me
something magical...
and when you see my
right hand negate it,
then you'll have
no other choice
but to believe
what I said.
Okay...! I can show
you something...
My robes...
They're magic.
These are known as
the Walking Church...
They create an impenetrable
protective barrier.
The Walking Church...?
What does that even mean?
You keep throwing
out these terms
like I'm supposed
to understand.
Well, sorry, but I don't.
Maybe a little experiment
will get it through
your thick head.
Take this knife and
try to stab me with it!
Wha... are you crazy?
Do I have to
explain everything?
These robes have
been sanctified
the same way as a church.
That means
they're as strong as
if they were an
actual building.
So while I'm wearing them,
you can take a stab at me
with this knife and it
won't injure me one bit.
Yeah, well... that's
interesting and all,
but I'm still not gonna
stab you with that thing.
Are you even
listening to me...?!
I am wearing an
exact replica
of the Shroud of Turin.
Its divine power to protect
is unquestionable...
It wards off and absorbs
any attack that's
made against me...
physical or magical.
Oh, I see...
From what you're saying...
if those robes of yours
really do have
supernatural powers...
then all I would
have to do is
touch them with
my right hand...
and that would be that.
That's assuming
that your power
actually works
the way you say.
All right then,
fine with me!
When it's over,
just remember...
You asked me to do this!
Okay... that's strange.
Well, what a surprise.
Nothing's happening.
What's wrong?
Oh... it's nothing...
Look at this...
You must've bitten
me a hundred times.
You're like a really big,
really angry mosquito.
I'm sorry.
Maybe we should just
forget about it...
That way...
You really expect me to forget
something like this...?
How much of an insensitive
jerk can you be?
Well, uh... I...
I thought it would be
easier not to talk about it.
I guess I'm pretty embarrassed
about what happened, too.
You're still a jerk.
She wasn't lying, then.
Her habit blew apart
when I touched it...
She must be involved
with supernatural powers
somehow or another.
All done!
Nice job... You look
like a pin cushion.
Who knows, maybe I'll
start a fashion trend.
Oh, crap... My class!
Sorry... I'm running late
for my remedial class...
What're you gonna do?
I can give you a key
if you wanna stay.
No... that's okay.
It's better if
I move on...
Otherwise, those people
will track me down here...
And I'm guessing
you'd prefer it
if your place didn't
get blown up.
Hey... wait!
Just a sec!
You wanna know
what I think?
About your power...
that right hand
of yours...
I think it cancels
out the grace of God
and everything that
goes along with it.
Your hand opposes the divine,
and without God's grace,
you're bound to meet with
ill fortune at every turn.
Rotten luck...
Well, if ya ask me...
being born with
that power of yours
is pretty much the most rotten
luck a person could have.
Index...
What now...?
Is there anywhere safe you
can go after you leave here?
If I stay in one place,
they're gonna find me.
-But how?
-Like I showed you before,
my habit is imbued
with magic...
and because of that magic,
they're able to
track my location...
It'll be okay, though...
If I can just make
it to the church,
they will offer me sanctuary.
Why didn't you tell me...?
Knowing all that, how can
I let you leave here?
Come, now...
Do you really wanna
be dragged down
into the depths
of hell with me?
Goodbye.
If you run into
any more trouble,
you know where
you can find me!
Yep...! I'll come back
when I'm hungry again.
What are these things?
Agathions?
Oh, crap... my class!
Academy City is pretty much
what it sounds like....
A city packed with colleges,
high schools, middle schools,
and elementary schools.
With a population of two
point three million,
it's one third the
size of Tokyo.
About 80% of the people
living here are students...
It's an unusual place
filled with unusual sights...
Like those cleaning robots
outside my place earlier...
Never a dull moment here.
All right everybody,
it's time to begin...
Welcome to remedial class!
I had a little spare time,
so I thought I'd write a pop
quiz for you to take today.
You'll want to do your
very best on it...
If your grade is poor,
you'll be playing a
game of no-eyed poker.
Oh yeah, I think I
remember that one...
She makes you play poker
with a blindfold on, right?
That's it. With
the added bonus
that you can't leave 'til you've
won ten hands in a row.
Ah, jeez...
The last time she
made us play that,
we were stuck here
almost until morning.
You're the exception
today, Kamijo.
You don't have enough
development points...
So you'll be
playing the game
whether you do well or not.
Our sweet teacher has totally
got a thing for you, man.
Are you too
blind to see it?
Shut up...
I don't think giving me
a lot of extra work to do
means she likes me.
Didn't you hear? She's
gonna keep you after school
to punish you...
You can't tell me that
doesn't sound kinda hot.
So you're a pervert
and a masochist...
a real stand-up guy.
There's a whole wide world of
lovely women out there...
Why would I wanna
limit myself?
You freak.
Quiet back there...!
Another word and you'll get
more than no-eyed poker...
There are some even
better games I know.
Do we understand
each other?
Rotten luck.
I wonder how
Index is doing.
She left her head dress
thing at my place.
And what was that
other thing she said...
something about a hundred
and three thousand books...
I didn't see a
single volume.
Weird... She swore she
was carrying them, but...
I bet she'll be back for
her stuff before long.
Teacher!
Kamijo is watching the
girls' tennis team
instead of paying
attention to you!
You made her cry...
It is now past
student curfew...
All students, please return
to your homes immediately.
It is now past
student curfew...
Unbelievable.
I was stuck after
class that late...?
Stupid luck.
Ah...! There he is!
I found you,
and this time...
Come back here!
Listen! I'm talking to you...!
Stop walking already!
Oh, well. If it isn't
the little bug zapper.
Don't call me that!
I have a proper name,
thank you very much,
and it's Mikoto Misaka!
I'll bet you've been
calling me bug zapper
behind my back ever since
we first met, haven't you?
Why are you here,
Zapper...?
You in remedial, too?
Remedial class? Never...!
I'm here to shock you full
of so much electricity
you'll twitch like a
frog struck by lightning!
If you have any last words,
say them now!
I'll pass.
I don't think so!
Well, now...
How ya doin'...
did that wake
you up a bit?
You ready to fight me?
Give it a rest...!
Thanks to your little
lightning storm yesterday,
all my electrical
appliances are fried...
I've got a fridge
full of rotten food!
It's your own fault
for pissing me off!
What could I
possibly have done
to make you this
mad at me...?
I didn't so much as
lay a finger on you,
even after you
attacked me!
Exactly...! You haven't
hit me a single time...!
With no points scored on
either side, this is a draw.
Huh?
Okay, whatever.
You win already.
Don't "whatever" me!
You should be taking
this seriously!
Oh...
you want me to take
this seriously?
Is this day over yet...?
First a fake sorceress,
and now a
trigger-happy esper.
A sorceress?
Message... Message.
Aggressive EM
discharge detected...
System malfunction identified.
You idiot!
What were you thinking
zapping stuff around here?
Shut up!
Hurry, we need to
get out of here!
The cleaning robots?
What now...?
There shouldn't be anything to
clean in front of my place.
That's just my luck...
I should've known.
Hey, Index....
What're you
doing out here?
You can't sleep there.
No way...
This looks...
like blood.
Please just stay
with me, Index!
What happened...?!
Why are you here...?
Who did this to you?
Oh... that was us...
as in sorcerers.
[Music]
Stiyl Magnus...
That's the dirty
sorcerer's name...
Who are these people...?
What do they want?
Next time, "Innocentius.
"When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.