In order to stop
Angel Fall,
we must either defeat
the spell's caster
or destroy the site
of the ritual.
Suspicious of Misha's
recent behavior,
Tsuchimikado and I followed her
to my parents' new home,
where she had gone with my
mother earlier in the day.
However, when we arrived,
we found a surprise
waiting for us.
[Music]
Dad...
You're back, huh...?
Did your mother
come with you?
So, you saw the house...
What do you think
about our new place?
Why the long face, son?
Is something the matter...?
Have you and your mother gotten
into a fight, or something?
I wanna know why.
I want to know...
Why did you get involved
with the occult?
Whoa, slow down.
What are you--
Don't play dumb!
Yeah... I know you're
mixed up in sorcery,
now I wanna know
the reason why!
Oh, is that what
you meant...?...
Give me a second to think.
Where should I begin?
Toma.... think back a bit
to when you were a kid,
there was a nickname
everybody called you by.
You remember what it was?
Everybody called you... Jinx.
For whatever reason,
one unlucky thing
after another always
seemed to happen
when you were around.
At first it was just your
peers, but in time,
even adults started
giving you a wide berth.
That was the reason
I decided to send you
to school in Academy City.
All the superstitious
people who surrounded us
back home were
terrified of you.
So I sent you to a world
that was devoid
of such superstitions...
or so I thought.
However... even though you
were in a city of science...
you began to be treated
the same way you always
had been at home...
Clearly, science couldn't
rid you of your bad luck,
but I had to keep searching
for something that could.
And so, in a last desperate
move, I turned to the occult.
Ludicrous, isn't it...?
I was so determined to eliminate
other peoples' superstitions
that I found
some of my own.
You blind idiot.
Yeah... I've got
rotten luck, all right...
Even so...
It's a part of who I
am, and I accept that.
You should accept it, too.
I still have to
walk my own path,
despite whatever bad
luck may come my way.
You were happy...
just the way you were?
Well, you were right...
I was blind.
By trying to help,
instead I threatened
to take your happiness
away from you...
Of course, I think a part
of me always knew
that collecting all of
those good luck souvenirs
wasn't going to change anything
for you in the end, anyway.
Good luck souvenirs?
That's right...
but don't worry.
I'm gonna give up
souvenir hunting now.
Wait... What are you
talking about...?
You are the person
responsible for
bringing on Angel
Fall, aren't you?
I don't know this
"Angel Fall."
What country does that
souvenir come from?
I have one more
question...
Do you know where Mom is
right now? Answer honestly.
You're the one who
insisted on following her
to the new house...
You would've had
a better idea
of where she is than I would.
He isn't aware
of the switch...
Which means, he is under
the influence of Angel Fall.
Hey, Misha!
Thanks a lot...
I really appreciate you
keeping my wife company today.
I know why you're
here, but stop.
It's true that
Dad's appearance
hasn't been switched
with anyone else's...
I know that seems
suspicious,
but he hasn't noticed the
changes in anybody else, either
So couldn't that mean--
Response to question...
self-explanatory.
Target acquisition
completed.
Personal opinion one...
the solution to the
problem is simple.
Misha... stop.
You're not supposed to kill
anyone without a divine order.
Or have you forgotten
even that principle?
I'll be taking over now...
Please get your father
safely away from here
as quickly as you
can manage it.
Misha has the
wrong impression...
my father's not--
We've all been
tricked...
Her name isn't Misha.
I made an inquiry to
the Russian Church...
As it turns out, they only
have one Kruezhev on file,
and her name is Sasha.
This is probably
just an assumed form
that she switched into.
I don't understand
what you're saying...
If she's not a member of
the Russian Orthodox Church,
who is she?
There are beings in this
world without a fixed gender.
Rather, they are portrayed
in mythology as having
aspects of both male
and female within them.
They hold great power...
power far beyond the realm
of human understanding...
One would never
randomly choose
to swap identities
with another being.
Can you back up...? I'm
not really following this.
Stop and think
for a moment...
Have you forgotten the
name by which we refer
to this devastating spell?
What happened?
Where's the sun?
I see what she's doing.
By turning day into
night like this,
she's enhancing her power.
Controller of the blue,
symbol of the water.
Guardian of the moon,
protector of the rear side.
Her name is...
"The Power of God."
A sweep... a deluge
of flaming arrows
that has burned out
entire civilizations.
You fell from Heaven
unexpectedly,
and you desire to return.
And to do so, you are
willing to destroy
the entire world?
Well, we can't
let that happen.
What do you mean "we?"
She wouldn't touch my
right hand, remember...?
Why was that...?
It must mean that Imagine
Breaker works on angels, too.
No. From this point on,
the fight against her
does not involve you...
Your place isn't
here right now.
There's something
more important
that I need you
to do for me.
You and your father
must destroy
the ritual site
used for the spell.
Do that, and it will
no longer be necessary
for the Power of
God to kill Mr. oya
or unleash the sweep.
But there isn't much time.
Hurry, before the
formula's complete
and it's too late.
I can't leave you.
I'm not planning on
sacrificing myself,
if that's what you're
worried about...
I'm counting on you.
I've seen you save a girl
from death once before,
so I'd be grateful
if this time
my life was
the one you saved.
What is this, son...?
Please, what's going on?
All right, Kanzaki.
I'll leave it to you now.
Hey!
I hope you're ready, because
now you have to face me!
It has begun. I will
employ my Single Flash
and speak my name.
Salvare Zero zero zero!
Well, at this point,
things don't really
seem to be going our way.
Sorry about this, Kami.
We've got a tough
decision to make.
It looks like we have to
offer someone as sacrifice
if we want to get this
situation under control.
What I'm doing is nothing
short of reckless...
I myself am aligned to
the church of the cross...
How can I hope
to destroy an angel
who is similarly aligned?
I must!
Fortunately, I am no
ordinary member
of the Church of the Cross.
I am one of the
Amakusa Puritans,
the independent form
of the church in Japan,
born from the intolerance
of the Edo period.
Amakusa Puritanism is a fusion
of several diverse religions.
Christianity
had been banned.
They merged their faith
with Shinto and Buddhism
to mask their beliefs
and avoid persecution.
A normal Church
of the Cross member
may not be able to
defeat an angel,
but one of the Japanese
Shinto sect can!
Japanese Shinto
is polytheistic.
Interestingly, it even
contains certain forms
for countering a god.
Included in the religion's
commandments
is the instruction never
to cause harm to a god.
Why would such a
law be necessary...?
Unless, of course,
someone had tried it before.
It makes no sense that I'm
still relatively unharmed
after facing an angel.
If this keeps up, it's going
to become a war of attrition.
And meanwhile, the sweep
will be carried out.
Please succeed in
this, Toma Kamijo.
Put a stop to Angel Fall
before it's too late!
What's wrong...?
Come on, wake up!
She's sleeping too deeply.
Did someone drug her?
Why would anybody do
such a thing to her?
Toma!
Would you explain
all this...?
Tell me what on earth
is going on here!
Listen carefully...
The way things stand, a
lot of people are gonna die...
The only way to
stop that from happening
is if we cancel
out Angel Fall.
I still don't understand
what you're saying.
-What is Angel Fall
-Areyou still playing dumb? !
At least show me where
the ritual site is hidden!
You've got it wrong,
Kami. Put him down.
Tsuchimikado?
Haven't you figured out
what's going on here yet?
Well... I guess
I can't blame you...
You're still pretty new
to all this magic stuff.
Wait... What do you mean?
Figured out what truth?
You mean my dad isn't
responsible for all this?
He isn't the one who
activated Angel Fall?
Not exactly.
Toya Kamijo is most
definitely the culprit.
However, he is completely
unaware of having done anything.
But how is that
possible...?
I thought you needed
a large ritual site...
that that was the only
way to invoke Angel Fall.
Yes. We already found
the ritual site...
It's your parents'
new house, Kami...
All the good luck charms,
the folk art, the statues,
the occult goods...
Individually, they have
no real significance ...
but if they're all
placed in the correct
feng shui arrangement,
it's a very different story.
When that happens, they
create a synergistic effect
and become a single,
immense power.
For example, remember
the red post box
that was in the foyer?
Red is an attribute
of the south...
Also, there was a water
guardian turtle
in the bathroom...
And metal guardian
white tigers
on the kitchen
counter, as well.
Add in three thousand
good luck charms
your dad had collected
from all over the world,
and suddenly your ordinary
house becomes a temple.
Strange as it sounds, when
your parents came to the beach
and left the house empty, the
ritual ground was complete...
it must have activated.
So, my dad built
it by accident?
Yes... it was a
simple accident...
Angel Fall is nothing more
than a spell created
by the coincidental
arrangement of some objects.
If we had interfered with the
set-up while we were there,
we could have invoked an
even more dangerous spell.
In order to cancel out the
magic of the ritual site,
we have to destroy the
whole thing in one go...
If we cannot...
then we'll have to destroy
the caster... my dad.
An unfortunate
situation...
but what else can we do...?
After all, I
can't use my magic.
In times like this,
the English Puritan Church
gives its followers some
very unsavory instructions.
I'm sorry, but
it's my job.
No, I won't let you!
Back off, Kami...
You'll just get
yourself hurt.
Toma, what is this? !
Stay behind me!
I don't accept this...
The church thinks they
can demand my dad be used
as a human sacrifice
to stop Angel Fall?
Well, that's too bad. They've
got another thing coming!
Toma!
It's over. Ya might
as well stay down there.
Wanna do something to me...?
then, by all means,
have at it...
But don't do anything
else to hurt my son!
Oh?
I'm dead serious.
If you harm so much as
another hair on Toma's head,
I swear you're
going to regret it!
Now you're just
bein' silly...
You can't actually believe
you'd be able to take me.
You're right. I don't...
I may not win,
but if you hurt Toma,
I'll inflict as much pain on
you as I can before I go down.
Have I made myself
clear enough...?
I am Toma's father.
Anyone who threatens
him will answer to me!
Don't do it, Dad.
Don't, get involved
Toma...! It's useless.
If you try to protect me,
none of us are getting
out of this mess alive.
That isn't true Dad!
I don't care
what it takes.
We are gonna
survive this...
'cause whatever happens,
I'm my father's son.
That's my boy...
If that's how this is
gonna play out, so be it...
I think we should make
it formal, don't you?
As of now, Toma
Kamijo is officially
the enemy of
Motoharu Tsuchimikado.
What d'you say...?
Had enough yet?
Toma!
-Dad...
-Takes care of that.
All right, everybody.
Prepare yourselves for
an amazing display
of honest-to-goodness
sorcery.
This room will act as our
humble stage for today.
The first order of business
is properly setting the stage.
With that taken care of,
allow me to introduce
you to my magic troupe.
Time to get to
work, you guys.
Suzaku...
Seiryu...
Genbu...
Byakko...
The pistol has
been assembled...
but we still need to
see about loading it.
Sorcery?
The spell we're
performing is like a gun:
made up of individual parts,
each with a
different function...
For the barrel of the
gun, we have a barrier.
For the bullet, we have
a shikigami spirit.
What's he doing...?
I thought Tsuchimikado said
he couldn't use magic anymore.
And for the trigger, I'll
be using my own hand.
Remember what
I said, Kami?
There's more than
one way to skin a cat
and the same goes
for Angel Fall...
One option is to kill
the spell's caster...
and the other is to
destroy the magic circle.
No, don't.
You know, Kami, when you
say stuff like that,
you remind me a
lot of Kanzaki...
If she knew I was
doing things this way,
she would do everything
in her power to stop me.
Exactly like you would...
I had to find a way to
prevent you from interfering.
Unfortunately, that meant
I had to beat you up ...
but let's look at the
bright side, shall we...?
Now I can use my magic to blow
the whole ritual site away.
Just stop it...
You don't have to do this.
I'm afraid I can't grant
that particular request, sorry.
If there's something you
should know about me by now...
it's that I'm a
big, fat liar.
I don't know how you managed
to do it, Toma Kamijo...
but now I owe
you another one.
Dad...! Wake up...! Dad!
Tsuchimikado...
There had to
be another way.
There had to be...
What good could
sacrificing yourself
like that do anybody?
Hey, what's
happening, Kami?
Long time no see.
You been hangin'
in there all right?
Huh? ... What's wrong...?
You're white as a sheet.
You look like you've
just seen a ghost.
How can you be here?
You used magic again and
you died, didn't you?
Ahh...
-that was a lie.
-Huh? !
My esper power is
Auto Regeneration.
I'm a Level Zero, but
I can still restore my body...
Between you and me,
I think I can use magic
a few more times
before I keel over.
It's kind of a pain
to explain it all,
so I just didn't bother.
Really? That's your reason?
How many more times
do I have to tell you
before you believe
me: I am a liar...
That bit about sneaking
into Academy City
to do spy work was a lie...
In reality, I'm a counter
spy and only pretending
to be on the side of the
English Puritan Church.
Actually, to tell the
truth, that's a lie, too...!
In fact, I'm a
freelance spy
hired by multiple
agencies for espionage.
Why, you little...
Oh, come on,
don't be like that.
All's well that
ends well, right...?
But, I thought you
might react that way,
so I brought some folks
along to help cheer you up.
I'm telling
you, it's true!
Hitotsui Hajime was standing
right there in the house!
It's my mom... for real.
How are you
feeling, Toma dear?
Uh...
okay, I guess...
I mean, I'm starting to
get kinda used to being here.
Oh my goodness, dear...
We can't have you
getting used to being
hospitalized, can we?
Good to see you, son...
I'm glad you're
looking better now.
Thanks, Dad...
You look better, too.
Well, our house is
completely gone now,
but I consider that a small
price to pay for your safety.
Huh? ...
What did you say...?
What's wrong with the house?
You know how we built a
new house just a while ago?
Well, apparently
it was blown to pieces
in some mysterious explosion.
Where'd Tsuchimikado go?
Well, these things
do happen...
It's not so big
a deal, really.
We can just stay
in the old house
until we can get
the new one rebuilt.
You guys still
have the old one?
Sort of...
We were just renting it
from somebody all these years...
but fortunately, they
haven't re-let it yet.
We may not have owned it,
but it was still our home.
We lived there from the
time we got married up
until we built
the new place.
You remember.
You were always groaning
about how cramped it was.
Yeah, that's right.
Toma...
Oh, hey, Index.
Is something wrong...?
Why are you just peeking
around the wall like that?
Yes something's wrong...
You strangled me
with your bare hands.
At the beach, you buried me
in the sand up to my neck.
Um... I promise I had a good
reason for doing all of that.
Then you nearly smooshed
me to death behind a door.
No fair! That one wasn't me!
I was on the floor in pain
and you just ignored me!
Uh, yeah, I guess
that one was me...
I mean--! Well... you see...
Damn my luck!
[Music]
A kid named Unabara
starts pestering Mikoto.
To keep him away,
she asks me to pretend
I'm her boyfriend.
Wait, me on a date
with bug zapper?
Next time, "Replica."
When science and magic cross
paths, a story is born.