I'm okay with
being a monster...
It's because I'm a monster
that I didn't die,
even after everything that
stone creature did to me.
And it's because
I'm a monster
that I'm able to stand
up to that giant
and take another
beating if I have to.
I will do it...
I will protect the
people I care about,
no matter what.
That's why I've made
peace with it all...
That's why I'm glad
to be a monster.
Damn it...! I'm not
gonna let it happen!
Wha...!
Kazakiri!!
She won't come to
such a senseless end.
I'm gonna do something!
[Music]
If you're looking for Ellis,
I sent him on ahead.
And unless I miss my guess,
he should be arriving
at his target right now.
Of course, maybe...
he's already taken care
of what I sent him to do.
Damn you...
Good, you're angry...
You can stay here
and fight me, then...
I let the girl
go on her way.
You mean Kazakiri?
You can defeat Ellis,
but you won't do
so well against me.
Simple. Because
I want to start a war.
So why are you so intent
upon stirring up trouble?
Science and magic are evenly
balanced at the moment,
aren't they...?
Why do this now?!
Espers can't use magic
without consequences.
When they do, it
destroys their bodies...
Were you aware of
that, I wonder?
I am.
Didn't you ever wonder
how we first found out
about that particular little
wrench in the works?
Twenty years ago,
the dual use of power was
attempted for the first time ...
A certain movement arose.
Its members were curious
about what would happen
if science and magic
were used together.
They tried to give
rise to a new crafter,
one who could combine
sorcery and psychic powers...
Can you guess the result?
Ellis has been my
companion for a long time.
He was an esper who was
brought to Academy City
by one of the factions
who wanted to experiment
with science and magic.
I'd been in charge of
teaching him spells,
and thanks to them,
he had become a mess.
Knights came to bring
down the facility
where we were working.
Ellis tried to buy
me time to escape...
He was struck by
a mace and died.
Our two kinds should've
remained segregated!
Magicians with magicians.
Scientists with scientists!
If we don't maintain
our separate domains,
the same thing will
happen again and again.
We'll lose more lives!
Please...! You're talking
at cross-purposes, here...
If what you want
is to save lives,
then why the hell are
you starting a war?!
No... that's not what you're
really trying to do, is it?
You just need to give
them a good scare.
For your purposes, all
you have to do is make it
so that a war
almost breaks out.
I suppose now you think you
have the right to judge me?
I won't take it from you.
Wipe that look
off your face!
The ground itself
is my ally...
And here we are, in a tunnel,
trapped beneath the earth.
This is my territory!
No! She's bringing
the whole place down?
Let it all crumble.
Let the earth rain down!
Damn...! What now?
If you know so
much, Toma...
When performing the ceremony
to create a Telesmatic Image
to be used as an idol for the
English Church of the Cross,
what role is played
by the direction
and the position
of the caster?
-That's it!
-Swallow up the fool!
Mix him into the mud!
The circles on the
walls and ceiling
are designed
to bury me alive.
I will crush you until your
body is no more than a memory!
Which means...
The circles on the ground
have a different purpose.
This circle...
isn't made to attack!
It's there to keep
her protected!
What?!
He stopped it?
Damn...
Damn you.
I have work to do...
I have to set the stage
for a war between the sides.
Academy City's guard has
grown lax in recent years...
Even the English Puritan Church
has become presumptuous
enough to allow their grimoire
index to be held elsewhere...
The stage is set just
as it was for Ellis.
His tragedy was because
of a situation like this.
If this blindness grows
to where it encompasses
all of Academy City along
with the entire Church...
What crap.
I get that you're angry...
I get that
you're grieving.
But even so...
What has Kazakiri
ever done to you?
Or Index, for that matter?!
How do you think you're
gonna make anything better
by having innocent people
pay for what's happened?
You don't understand.
Damn it...
it would be easier
to just kill all the
sorcerers and scientists.
But it's more
complicated than that...!
If I had a choice,
I wouldn't want the two sides
fighting each other
any more than you do!
But from the
very beginning...
all of this had
me so conflicted!
I'm torn in so
many directions...
I don't know
which to choose.
Then why complicate it...?
You've always had
one true conviction.
Your direction hasn't
changed at all.
At your core...
everything you did
was because you regretted
the loss of your friend.
Did you ever stop to look at
my relationship with Index?
We're from separate
sides, you know.
Did you think our
friendship was doomed
because we didn't preserve
our own territories?
We could live
together forever
and nothing like
that would happen.
Ask yourself...
What gives you the right
to take my friend away?!
Intimus 115!
What?!
I was right.
You told me how conflicted
you were for a reason.
You'll see, esper.
I'm going to destroy you!
I understand what
you're doing now.
Somewhere inside, what
you desperately want...
is for somebody to stop you!
This isn't good...
He switched from
remote to self-control.
I can't intercept anymore!
Nothing...
Can... reach my
dear Ellis now.
Ellis...
Kazakiri...
Index...!
Toma...
Hyoka?!
What's... that?
Run!
Hurry and get
out of here...
It's too dangerous...
You have to go.
The golem is out
of control...
He may not be able to
manage his regeneration.
Come on! Let's get
out of here, Hyoka!
I need to stay...
You get out of here.
What do you mean stay...?
What are you
planning to do?
I... have to
stop the monster.
No you can't...!
You don't seriously believe
you can defeat that thing,
do you Hyoka?
If you fight it head on,
there's no way you'll survive!
It's all right...
I'm no more human than
this stone monster.
I'm really sorry...
for not telling you
about it 'til now.
Hyoka!
To fight a monster,
you have to send a monster...
I accept that now.
I can never go back to
that place in time...
I'm so glad it happened,
but it isn't where I belong.
But even so...
I won't sacrifice the
memory without a fight!
Hyoka!
I have to...
Index is my friend!
Kazakiri!!
Toma!
I told you.
I told you I was
gonna prove that
it didn't matter
if you're human.
You're still our friend!
And I won't let
it end like this!
It's over...
The illusion is done...
but it was so nice
while it lasted.
Whoa... what a mess!
What in the world
went on here?
Oh, let me guess...
This is your doing.
I suppose I should be
getting used to it,
but I'm still curious...
how much trouble
are you in this time?
Is... is something wrong?
Oh, Sissy, I've
been so worried.
Where have you...
This is quite a mess...
Are you responsible?
No, of course not!
Given the state
of this place,
Judgment or Antiskill
will be here before long...
Let's go before
there's any trouble...
Did you hear me?!
I told you,
I didn't have anything...
I knew all along...
I knew that things
would turn out this way.
I mean, I'd have to
be an idiot not to...
How else could I expect
other people to respond
when they found out
what I really am?
It isn't what I wanted,
you know, not at all...
but what other choice
could I have made?
She's my friend...
the only person who has ever
called me their friend before...
so I wanted to save her.
But I wish...
I wish I didn't have to
lose her now, that's all.
I wish... she didn't
have to be afraid of me.
I... I had to...
I had to...!
I couldn't stand to see
my friend get hurt...
so I showed her
that I'm a monster.
There was no other way.
I just stood up to that
giant with all I could.
I wanted us to be
friends forever...
We got along so well,
I was so sure we could be...
but now...
Now that obviously isn't
going to happen, huh...?
I made that sacrifice...
I had to save her...
Even if she hates me...
I couldn't stand
by and let her die!
Does it hurt?
Are you sad?
If that's the case...
then you're no
monster at all.
As far as I know,
monsters don't experience
any emotions...
You're just as
human as I am...
and you can quote me on that.
And one more thing.
Some friendships don't
go away that easily.
She's here?
But how...?
There's no way...
This must just be
another illusion.
I'm just a thing,
a creature.
How can she be looking
at me like that...?
That's the kind of
way you look at someone
you really care about...
You don't get
that angry...
unless you're a friend...
Unless you know
you'll make up.
So maybe you're a
little strange...
Your body's put
together differently
than other peoples' are...
and you can do some things
the rest of us can't...
So what?
Hyoka!
We're all weird
in our own way...
And it looks to me like
you're still Index's friend...
wouldn't you say?
Are you happy
with yourself?
You are now even closer
to the completion of a key
to controlling the Imaginary
Number School District's
Five-Element Agency.
Honestly, sometimes I wonder
just what exactly
you're up to.
You figured out that the
Imaginary Number School District
was actually an
AIM diffusion field.
Who would dream that up?
Then you take it
a step further
and plant a sense of self into
the key to help it materialize?
Are you crazy or a genius...?
I'd really like to know what
you're thinking, Aleister.
Hold on...
The Imaginary Number
School District
is an accumulation of power
that exists in a different
realm than humanity.
The life that is formed as
the result of that power...
Such a life...
can only be
called one thing.
An angel.
And if there is a whole city
like the Imaginary
Number School district
populated by beings
like Kazakiri...
beings who can only be
referred to as angels...
that means...
So that's what you're
doing, you old schemer.
You're creating an artificial
Heaven, aren't you?!
You'll find that I have no
comment on such topics
as Heaven and angels.
Oh, that's rich...
There's no one who knows
more about it than you do.
So don't even try,
Crowley the Sorcerer.
This incident's been designed
to gradually derail the
stability of the world...
You lured a member of the
English Puritan Church here,
and then saw to it that
she was gotten rid of.
I don't pretend to know
your ultimate plan.
However...
If you're going to keep using
Imagine Breaker, be prepared.
He doesn't like people who
go against his convictions,
and that right hand could devour
your world with its power.
Regrettably...
the world that I believed in
fell apart a very long time ago.
That's right,
take a good look.
I didn't even have to be
hospitalized this time...!
Man, am I awesome or what...?
I think this shows that
I've made some progress...
Don't you agree?
Enough gloating...!
You really have no
grasp on reality!
Do you have any idea
how much trouble you
cause for other people
when you get yourself into
these scrapes Kamijo?!
Bothering Antiskill with
your antics is a new low,
even for you!
I believe I told you to be
careful around Hyoka Kazakiri...
How explicit do
I have to be?
You seem to perpetually
get into trouble
whenever you're
around girls...
Perhaps you should consider
a psychological evaluation
at some point.
Um, Doctor...
I feel that my life is being
threatened at the moment.
Perhaps I could
check myself in...?
You know, with orders for
peace and quiet and no visitors?
Um, Index...
Your skirt is kind of...
Aren't you
going to fix it?
Does it really
look that weird?
Yes, it is
sort of weird...
It's very weird,
in fact...
It was strange
when I first saw it...
but now I think
it's even more strange.
You're saying
I look strange.
That was strange...
Hyoka...?
Yeah.
The best way I can explain
is that my body is like a
big mass of psychic energy.
Nothing I do will
change the fact
that I'm an unstable being.
That's just the
way I was created.
Is that why you couldn't
touch Toma's right hand?
Mm-hmm.
I couldn't come in
contact with it at all...
After even a
second-long touch
I would've vanished
without a trace.
Oh, there's
something else.
I did notice something
about his power...
I don't think I know how to
put it into words, exactly...
But I know there's
something more to it
than just esper ability.
All right, then.
Hyoka...?
Sorry, Index...
I have to go now.
Don't go!
Come on, there's
nothing to worry about.
Don't forget that my
body is composed
of the combined powers
of many different people.
I may disappear
for a while.
But it's not
like I'm dying...
It just means that you
won't be able to see me.
But even though you
might not know it...
I'll always be
by your side...
no matter what happens.
Hyoka!
Promise me...
We'll have fun
together again.
Of course!
[Music]
The thing is I'm really busy
during second term you know?
But what am I supposed to do?
I'm dying of
boredom, here!
Toma's all busy and not
paying attention to me, jerk!
So you see this
is what people mean
when they say
someone is magic...
Pretty sexy,
don't you think?
Right, Hime, you can be
sexy like that, can't you?
I see... like this?
All right, kids!
Let's get class started
without further delay!
Huh? Where's Tsuchimikado
this morning?
Yeah, that's right...
Don't worry about it.
I'm on it.
So my job is to look
after these two?
Please. I would appreciate that.
Oh... How careless of me...!
My ribbon's drifting
into the shower,
right where Sissy is!
Kuroko!
There is a situation
which requires the assistance
of the grimoire index.
Have her "manager"
come as well, please.
"Manager,"... sure...
I'll see that it's done...
Kanzaki and I should
be able to leave soon.
About that...
We've been unable
to reach Kanzaki.
What do you mean, Archbishop...?
Is she out of touch?
Mmm... Given the
way I am attired,
you needn't
address me as such.
We can forego the title.
My name is Laura Stewart...
For now, I think
that will suffice.
Um... hello?
You still alive there?
Just barely...
You forgot that the refrigerator
was a desolate wasteland,
didn't you, Toma?
And you were going to eat that
sandwich all by yourself, eh?
No, no, this isn't what
it looks like at all!
Oh? Because it looks like
you have food and I don't!
I'm hungry,
do you hear me?!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
Stupid luck!