The first day
of summer vacation
turned out to be
an eventful one...
A young sister
calling herself Index
showed up hanging
from my balcony railing.
She said she
was being chased
by some sort of
magical society.
But that's absurd...
This is Academy City,
a town of science,
not magic!
[Music]
Innocentius
The Witch Hunter King
No way...
This looks like...
like blood.
Please just stay
with me, Index!
What happened...?!
Why are you here...?
Who did this to you?
Oh... that was us...
as in sorcerers.
And it looks like they've
done a really ugly number
-on her again.
-But why?
First ask what her reason
was for returning ...
Perhaps she came back here
because she left
something behind.
She was wearing a
hood yesterday...
Now, where could that
have gone, I wonder?
They tracked the magical
power of the hood
back to my place.
Come now...
Do you really
wanna be dragged down
into the depths
of hell with me?
She risked her own life to
come back here for the hood...
just to keep
a total stranger
from getting caught
up in her trouble.
How could she
be so foolish?
Oh, calm down...
There's no need
to look at me
like I'm some
kind of a monster.
I'm not the one who
carved her up like that...
and I'm fairly certain
that Kanzaki didn't mean
to make such a bloody
mess of her flesh, either.
Her habit is a
Walking Church.
It should provide
absolute defense.
And yet somehow
it got all torn up.
How could you?
Magic has never
seemed like any more
than a fairy tale to me...
and I don't put
much stock in the idea
of a magical society.
But you... You
look human enough.
Don't you know the difference
between right and wrong?
A little girl comes
here for her hood...
You and your friends
hunt her down like a dog...
and do this to her...
Is your soul so utterly
corrupt you can't understand
how wrong what
you've done is?
If you're finished
with your lecture,
could you please step aside...?
I'm here for that.
For...
"that?"
Well... "those"
to be accurate...
The grimoires...
The hundred and three
thousand very important
volumes young Index
carries with her everywhere.
You really should
be more careful...
Those books can be
extremely dangerous...
Reading so much
as a single volume
would cripple a boy
such as yourself.
Look... I'm tired of
being screwed with...
Where are these
supposed books?
They're right there...
next to you...
Inside her head.
Index is one of the few people
with a photographic memory...
She only has to
see something once
and it's memorized
word-for-word inside her head.
Essentially, her
brain's a library...
The grimoires
are locked safely
in places around the world...
but she's read them all
and stored their
contents in her mind.
But as she herself
doesn't have the power
to conjure magic
she remains harmless.
As I have already
told you though,
the volumes that she carries
are a bit dangerous...
So, I'm here...
We had to locate her
so we could take charge
of the grimoires.
We wouldn't want them to
fall into the wrong hands.
Take... charge...?
That's right...
I'm here... to take her...
get it...?
It doesn't matter how
honest and loyal she is.
Anyone can be broken if
tortured for long enough.
Think of this poor girl
in the hands of people
who'd do anything
to know what she knows.
Breaks your
heart, doesn't it?
Why, you...! Who do
you think you are? !
I'm Stiyl Magnus...
At least, that's
one of my names...
but for our
current purposes,
I am Fortis
Nine Three One.
The former actually
translates to "mighty one."...
but... its etymology
doesn't matter.
I've said my magic name.
Do you know
what that means?
We sorcerers
don't generally
give out our magic names...
Those names serve to
limit our power...
but when they're
spoken to another,
that limitation vanishes.
I spoke my name to you...
Now you understand the
significance of that...
Among my kind,
they're known as...
killer names... so...
Flames!
Impossible...
is this magic?
It's so strong...
Will my power work against
something like this?
I know it can cancel out
supernatural esper powers...
but this?
I've never seen anything
like it before...
Who knows what
will happen.
Here, I've brought a little
parting gift for you.
I may have overdone
it a little bit...
Not my cleanest work...
One thing's
certain, though...
There's no chance he
survived an attack like that.
Oh, really?
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
Here I am.
Impossible!
Jeez... I'm an idiot.
There was no reason
to be scared...
I have seen it work
on magic before this...
My right hand
destroyed her robes.
Damn you!
All right...
I understand it now.
You did it. You were the one who
destroyed the Walking Church.
One of the five elements
that make up the known world.
The first light that
pierced the darkness.
The light whose presence
can provide comfort and warmth.
And whose judgment brings
the destruction of the wicked.
It has the power to give
life and to take it away.
It is fierce...
It is hungry...
It is cruel.
I call upon fire...
to serve as my sword...
Manifest thyself
and feed upon me
that thou shall gain power!
This is the Witch
Hunter King, Innocentius...
Also known as...
Absolute destruction.
Take this!
Why isn't my hand
working against it?
These flames....
They keep coming back as
soon as I snuff them out.
Runes.
Magic words...
They have been used
by Germanic tribes
since the second century...
There are twenty-four
letters...
They signify arcane mysticism
and secret knowledge...
and are the roots
of Old English.
Attacking Innocentius
will have no effect...
The walls... the floor...
the ceiling.
As long as the rune seals
engraved nearby remain intact,
he will continue
to regenerate.
Index...! Is that you?
That is correct...
I am the
library of grimoires
belonging to Necessarius.
Also known
as the zeroth parish
of the English Puritan Church...
My formal name is Index
Librorum Prohibitorum...
but if you prefer,
you may shorten that
and refer to me
merely as Index.
I am currently invoking
an automatic program
known as John's Pen.
You're out of luck.
Eliminating all the runes
that have been engraved
on this building
will be impossible...
There's no point in
even attempting it.
Ashes to ashes...
And dust to dust!
Prepare for
the wrath of...
Squeamish Blood Rood!
Damn!
This is it. I'm
going to... die.
Okay, maybe
I'm not dead yet.
What the... What are those?
I think they're
rune engravings!
I'm dead!
Damn!
Why did it stop
following me?
I get it... It's the runes...
they're only
posted in the dorm.
I should probably
call someone.
There's gotta be a
phone around here.
I have to go for help...
I am not running away.
Do you really
wanna be dragged down
into the depths
of hell with me?
I've gotten myself
into a huge mess...
all for a girl I just
met this morning.
What am I thinking?
So foolish...
Does he really think this
will extinguish Innocentius?
I'm soaking wet
because he decided
he wanted to play firefighter.
What happened
to Innocentius?
Wow, man... You
almost had me...
It was a real
close call...
Lucky for me you didn't
carve those runes
with a knife or anything...
I wouldn't have
stood a chance then.
You idiot...
Innocentius' fire burns
at three thousand degrees...
This little shower won't
put out his flames.
Yeah... I know...
that wasn't the
idea, though.
You know, it's
rude to plaster stuff
on other peoples' homes.
That's a nice try.
But you didn't think it
through well enough...
It's not like those runes
were written on toilet paper.
A little water's not
going to dissolve them...
Now, I think it's
time for you to admit
you're out of your league.
Kill him.
This doesn't make sense...!
My runes should still be
working at full strength.
The ink.
Of course the paper
didn't dissolve...
The ink's your problem...
It tends to run
when it gets wet.
I have to find
Innocentius.
Innocentius!
Now then, sorcerer...
Ashes to ashes...
And dust to dust...
I call on the power of
Squeamish Blood Rood.
All right, Index,
I've made my decision.
I don't wanna be
dragged into hell.
So that leaves
me one choice.
I'll free you
from its clutches.
Using this!
There you are!
Oh, finally! I've been looking
for you everywhere!
I knew there was no way
you were kept late
for remedial class, and
sure enough, here you are,
out enjoying all the pleasures
the night has to offer!
Gimme a break, Kuroko.
Exactly what part of
this makes it look like
I'm out for a leisurely
night on the town?
Oh, I can answer
that easily...
This place isn't on your
way home from school.
The fact that you're
here at all means
you took a detour
for some reason.
Well... I had to run an errand
in this part of town...
And why are you
here, anyway?
Oh right... I'm here on
official business...
for Judgment ...
Something strange
happened tonight.
I came to investigate.
The fire wasn't natural...
It had to have
been cause by someone
with psychic abilities.
That should keep
them from using it as
some kind of magical
tracking device.
Before I do anything else,
I need to get
her to a hospital.
And after that...
then what...?
I doubt she has any
kind of ID on her...
A foreign nun with
no identification...
word will get
out in no time.
Still... I have no choice.
I can't just
leave her alone.
Toma...
Is something wrong...?
You look so tired and pale.
You're worried
about me...?!
We need to do something
about your injuries!
I'll be all right...
Really...
It's not bad...
If we can just
stop the bleeding,
I... I've got you!
Hey... what about those
books you've got
crammed in your brain...?
Is there any magic in there
that can heal injuries?
Yes... there is.
Let's use it!
You couldn't perform it.
Even if I was able to
teach you the spell...
and even if you
performed it perfectly,
down to the last detail...
your power
would interfere.
Damn... Damn...!
Not again...!..
It always comes back
to my stupid hand!
It isn't because of
your right hand...
It's the esper power
that you have
that would interfere
with the spell.
Some espers are born with
their psychic abilities,
and some develop
them over time...
Magic isn't a power
one can be born with,
but something
that is learned.
It was created by people
who saw the espers
and desired power
of their own...
Magic and psychic ability
are mutually exclusive.
So... all of the
students who live here,
working to develop their
psychic abilities...
Right... they
can't use magic.
Damn it...!
That can't be right!
It seems so unfair...!
What do we do now?
We have a whole city
of talented students...
but they can't do magic.
The students can't do it...
But... Wait...
What about the others...?
Can people who don't have
any esper talent use magic?
It would be my rotten luck that
she's already gone to sleep.
I guess I'll have to
be more aggressive...
Here goes.
Yes, yes, I'm coming...
No use banging
like that...
If you haven't noticed yet,
it's a very sturdy door...
Useful for keeping
salesmen out.
Kamijo...! What
are you doing here?
You haven't taken a job as a
door-to-door salesman, have you?
What kind of salesman
carries a Sister
on his back when he's
out on his rounds...?
Listen, my friend and I
are in a bit of trouble...
Do you think we can
come inside...?
-Thank you. We'd appreciate it.
-Hey, hold on a second!
You can't just barge in
on a person like this!
I wasn't expecting
company tonight.
The place is a
bit of a mess...
We all have our
vices, you know?
Whoa...! What happened
here...? Poor thing!
I need your help... See--
What's going on?
Urgent warning...
Read from Chapter
2, Verse 6...
Excessive loss of
blood has resulted
in a significant depletion
of life force...
as a result...
John's Pen has been
auto-activated.
I have run calculations
based on heart rate
and extent of blood loss.
The data indicates that
with no change in status,
I will have fifteen more
minutes before my body
loses its minimum
life force...
Should that occur,
I will perish.
I would appreciate it if you
would follow my instructions
and take the steps necessary
to ensure my survival.
Here's what we'll do...
Listen... I'll go call
an ambulance...
and you follow whatever
instructions she gives...
Please, Teacher We
have to save her....
don't let her lose
consciousness while I'm gone.
She's a Sister, and only
we can help her right now...
Will you?
Good... All right, Index...
It's settled.
Is there anything else
I can do to help you?
No, there is not...
Unfortunately, under
the circumstances
the only option is for you
to vacate this place entirely.
Your presence will
cause interference...
If you remain, your power
will cancel the recovery magic.
Um... did I hear her
right...?
Did... did the Sister really say
something about recovery magic?
She did.
Please, take
good care of her.
Kamijo! I have a
phone right there!
Unfortunately, under
the circumstances
the only option is for you to
vacate this place entirely.
Your presence will
cause interference...
If you remain, your power
will cancel the recovery magic.
[Music]
Hold on...
They're gonna use magic
to call down an angel...?
Is that what it will
take to heal Index?
Next time, "Necessarius."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.