Great... nosebleed.
There's a good reason
why I'm sleeping
in the bathroom every
night lately.
Ow!
Tissue...
My bed, where I
should be sleeping,
is currently occupied
by someone else:
my rather odd houseguest.
I miss my soft,
comfortable bed...
but mostly I try not to
think about it too much.
Toma...?
Oh, sorry...
Did I wake you up?
Yes, you did...
So, tell me...
what're you doing here, near
the bed where I'm sleeping,
instead of where
you're supposed to be?
What am I doing here?
Well, I just...
Had a nosebleed...
Wait...! Don't get
the wrong idea here.
Arousal only causes
nosebleeds in manga!
Toma!
I want you to swear
on our Father,
who art in Heaven...
Did you feel nothing when you
gazed upon my sleeping face?
Whoa, what are
you talking about?
You were just laying
there, sleeping.
Of course I didn't
feel anythi--
What do you mean, you
didn't feel anything? !
I may be a nun, but I'm
still a girl, you jerk!
I refuse to believe that
the sight of me in the bed
didn't affect you at
least a little bit.
-Just admit it!
-Yes, I admit it!
I solemnly swear that my heart
began to race when I saw you.
There, are you happy now?
Oh, no. After your
earlier reaction,
you're going to have to
do a lot more than that
to convince me!
I feel like there's something
I might be forgetting....
There are only twenty-four hours
of summer vacation left...
The teachers always assign
homework over the break,
just to make sure you
can't actually relax.
And... I'm fairly certain...
I didn't do any of it.
Rotten luck.
[Music]
The very last day of
summer vacation is here!
Misaka! Misaka!
You don't seem up to much.
Are you being lazy?
Yeah, of course...
I'm on summer vacation.
But you're studying
to be a maid.
Shouldn't you avoid
chit-chatting?
Hey, if you're
going to the store,
do you think you could
pick up a manga for me?
I like ones that have
romance in them,
but don't get too
steamy, you know?
So, basically...
you're looking for
a romantic comedy?
Yeah, boy meets girl,
boy loses girl,
boy gets girl back, and everyone
lives happily ever after!
Yeah, okay.
Hey. Good morning.
How lucky that I ran
into you, Misaka...
So, where are
you headed to?
I would be more than
happy to walk with you
part of the way if you
don't mind some company.
Oh, Unabara...
Good morning.
Huh? You look
a little pale.
Do you think you might be
coming down with something?
Oh...
No.
What's wrong with
this guy...?
He hasn't left me alone a
single day this week.
I know this great little
seafood restaurant
that's just around
the corner.
Maybe we could grab
a bite to eat there.
I just had breakfast and
he's inviting me to lunch?
Oh... ...
I appreciate the
invitation and all,
but I have some
errands I need to run.
Okay, I'll come with you.
Well... I'm actually going
to buy some lingerie,
and that's kind of an awkward
place to bring a guy,
so goodbye.
I don't mind at all.
Now what do I do...?
I can't tell him I'm
going to the store
to look at comic books.
Please! I'm begging you!
Sorry, Kami, no way...
I've got a private lesson
scheduled with Miss Komoe,
and I'm not gonna miss it.
It's just that helping
you out with your homework
isn't gonna get
us any action...
If there were chicks involved,
it would be different.
That's it. I'll pretend I was
waiting for someone else!
Oh, hey...!
Been waiting long?
Of course that's
all we care about!
Tall girls, short girls,
thin girls, fat girls,
blonde girls, stupid
girls, smart girls,
girls with curly hair,
girls with straight hair,
I said, "Been
waiting long?"...
Stop ignoring me!
Damn... Ow...
Who the--?
Oh, Zapper? !
I beg you. Just play along.
Anyway, so sorry
I'm late...
Let me make it
up to you, okay?
Today, lunch
will be my treat!
Sound good?
Lunch?
How interesting...
a secret rendezvous in
front of the girls' dorm.
Hooking up with a boy and not
telling me first, Sissy?
That's unacceptable!
Hey, what's the
big idea...?
Dragging me away from my friends
without bothering t--
-Shut up!
-What?
Please, just stop talking
and give me a second to
collect myself, all right?
So, basically,
this Unabara guy
has been following
you around the whole week
and you're sick of it?
That's pretty much it...
Apparently, he's the grandson
of our school's director,
so I can't just
blow him off.
So... you needed somebody to
pretend to be your boyfriend,
and I just
happened to be around?
What choice did I have...?
You were passing by.
I seized the opportunity.
Well, you've gotten
away from him for now,
haven't you...?
So there's no real reason
we need to keep up
this act anymore.
Well... I'd really
like to make sure
that he thought
I was off-limits
and never
bothered me again,
but that would mean...
That would mean
what, exactly?
You're going to have to stick
by my side all day today...
We need as many people
as possible to see us.
That should convince Unabara--
What's wrong with you?
Just my luck.
Well... if you have
a better idea,
I'd like to hear it.
A better idea, huh...?
Yeah, I've got one.
Why don't you try wiping
the mustard off your face?
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I-I'm fine.
Why do you ask?
Hey... Which one's yours
and which one's mine?
Well, um... I think
maybe this one is--
Let me look at it!
Huh?
You figure it out yet?
-I said
-No, they look exactly the same!
Here, you take this one.
We'll just have
to hope it's right.
Honestly...! Are you
always this careless...?
Freaking idiot!
Hey, it's not like
it's my fault
you ordered both of
us the same thing.
Uh... what's
bothering you now...?
I've never seen you
this quiet before.
Nothing's wrong. I'm fine.
So... what's our
next move gonna be?
Huh? ...
What do you mean, "move?"
You know what I mean...
How do we make
everybody believe
that we're the real deal?
So, now that the
experiment is over,
fewer than ten of the Sisters
are still living
in Academy City.
Most of them are staying
in an institution
to have their
bodies readjusted.
What a relief.
It sounds like
everything turned out for
the best in the end...
I'm glad to hear
they're okay.
Uh-huh...
I'm guessing this isn't what
couples normally talk about.
Yeah... you're probably
right about that.
Oh, perfect...
Instead of paying
attention to me,
you're going to study...
That totally makes it look
like we're a happy couple.
What more do you
want from me?
I need to get this
homework done...
I have to turn it in in
less than twenty-four hours.
Homework, huh...?
Yeah... I've heard
of that before.
Wait... Does your school
not give out homework?
Come on... let me see
what you're doing.
Uh... all right...
Oh, okay.
So this is just a basic
math review, then.
Wow... how do you
know all that?
How do you not
know all this?
Hey! Hey...!
How about we just take a little
breather and get a soda...?
I'll go pick us
up some, 'kay?
No, no...
I'll do it.
I said I was going to
pick them up, so I will...
When I've made up my mind,
it's not good to disagree.
Pleased to meet you...
uh...
Oh, I'm Toma Kamijo.
My name's Mitsuki Unabara.
So... what can I do for ya?
Uh... Well, I was
just wondering
if you were a
friend of Misaka's.
That a problem?
Sort of...
I'm not really
crazy about guys
being friends
with the girl I like.
I guess I just wish
she'd be more clear about
who she likes and
who she doesn't...
That's not asking too
much, is it...?
Oh, the answer to that
question is three.
Really...? I always found
she's pretty upfront
about her feelings.
Lucky you...
When I talk to her
I get the sense
she isn't telling me
the complete truth
about how she feels...
Oh, and, the answer
to that one is four.
They put the two
there to trick you.
Uh... yeah, I think
you're right. Thank you.
Not a problem.
I'm happy to help.
What's the
matter with you?
Can I speak with
you for a moment?
It's not gonna
do me any good
if you're just gonna
make friends with him...!
Remember... as of
today you're my boy...
You're pretending
to be my boyfriend
so we can get mister Unabara
to leave me alone for good.
It's not like its rocket
science or anything!
-I can't.
-Huh?
Well, he's actually
a really nice guy...
and I think he's
serious about you.
What do you mean?
I don't get what it is you
don't like about him...
Well... I guess
it's your choice;
you can always
tell him 'no'.
Listen, you...!
You're right...
Just forget about it.
So... what do we do now...?
Are we keeping
this up still?
-Or maybe you...
-No!
You can stop pretending
to be my boyfriend
but let me treat you
to one last thing.
What do you feel like?
We're already
eating again?
Everywhere looks full.
How about there...?
That'll work...
Stay here, I'll
get us something.
Misaka, hold up!
What's this...?
Are you alone?
Did you get all your
homework finished up?
Yeah... If you're looking
for Misaka, she's in there.
What? Is there
something wrong?
You wouldn't happen
to have a twin brother,
by any chance would you?
No... No brothers or sisters.
That's weird...
Someone who looks like you
just ran into the restaurant.
Whew...! It's so hot!
Hey what are you doing?
You have to get
out of here!
Sorry, you said someone
who looks similar to me
just went into
that restaurant?
Not "similar."
This guy looked like
he could be your
identical twin.
There are espers who can
alter their appearance
to look like other people...
One could've made
himself look like me
to get close to Misaka.
Huh... I didn't realize
she was such a celebrity.
Would you mind
checking it out...?
I'd go, but I think
I upset her earlier.
Uh... sure...
You wait here.
I guess there is a
flaw in every plan...
How inconvenient for me.
I didn't think the real
Unabara could escape.
You mean you're not him?
That was magic!
Damn it!
Okay, I get it...
So this TV show
"Magical Powered Kanamin"
is about a girl who can fool
the Roman Orthodox
Witch Hunter Crusaders
by simply disguising
herself as a student.
But why does she need a
rainbow-colored wand to do that?
Yes, hello?
Is everything
all right there?
I think we've got
another sorcerer in town.
What's wrong...?
It sounds like you're
running from someone!
Yeah!
Can you describe him?
His clothes,
weapons, behavior?
The knife he carries
is made of obsidian...
I know it...
I think it might be
The Spear of
Tlahuizcalpantecuhtli.
Tlah... What?!
An Aztec god.
His name means Lord
of the House of Dawn...
The spear is said
to kill anyone
who is bathed in
the light of Venus.
Never mind the background,
just tell me
what I should do!
I just need to know
how I'm supposed to
get rid of this guy!
Quickly!
The sorcerer just has
a replica of the spear.
It's probably a mirror.
He'll attack by reflecting
the light from Venus
in the spear's
obsidian blade.
I think the best
thing for you to do
is to try blocking it
with your right hand.
Okay.
Is he using this Aztec magic
to disguise himself as Unabara?
Aztec priests would
flay the skin
of a human sacrifice
and then wear it.
I'm guessing
this is analogous.
Wait--they do what
with the skin?
First they'd strip it
off with a knife...
and then they'd wear it.
If he's just using
it as a disguise,
it's possible he took only
a small portion of skin
and used it to
change his appearance.
Man, these sorcerers
are twisted! Hmph...
Toma!
Time to say your prayers!
Impossible...!
I'm sure the knife was
positioned perfectly!
Cement dust?
Damn it!
Now then...
I have a question.
Why did you pick Unabara's
body as your disguise...?
To get close to Misaka...?
Why her? She has nothing
to do with magic.
Hah...! You're not joking.
You really don't
get it, do you?
What?
You have access to the
one hundred and three
thousand grimoires...
And as if that
wasn't enough,
you've made friends with some
interesting people lately...
Among them are a few
sorcerers and a Level 5 esper.
You're forming a
group of supporters
being referred to as
The Kamijo Forces.
The what?
Dude... You're
not making sense.
Your friends...
Together, their
power threatens
to upset the balance
between the two worlds.
You're not the only one I'm
targeting for extermination...
I want every member
of the Kamijo Forces.
My plan was to use the faces
of people familiar to you
to erode your trust and
destroy you from the inside out.
Sneaky punk.
Unfortunately, Mitsuki
Unabara's identity
is useless to me now.
I'll have to use somebody
else's body as my disguise.
You don't mean...
You were going
to use Misaka?
-You...!
-Oh, no.
I think your face will
suit my purposes perfectly.
I liked you...
I actually thought that
we could be friends.
Really...?
Because I never thought
anything like that about you.
You could've fooled me...
and what about all that stuff
you said about liking Misaka...?
You were probably just
faking that, too, weren't you?
Don't judge me for what
you can't understand.
I am a fake, but that
doesn't change the fact
that I wanted
to protect Misaka.
This stupid stunt wasn't
my plan to begin with!
But then...
my superiors determined
that the Kamijo Forces
were too dangerous!
Then you...
If you had just been
less troublesome...
If you had just backed down
and made it possible
for me to report
that you weren't a threat...
we wouldn't be here,
and I wouldn't have
had to trick Misaka!
Wow...
You're actually in love
with her, aren't you?
Yes... but you're
her friend,
and now I'm your enemy.
I don't have a choice.
That face isn't yours.
It's an illusion that
I'm gonna destroy!
Move, quick!
It looks like...
I've lost this fight.
Yes, you have.
I won't be the last one
they send after you
and your group.
Like it or not,
you and Misaka will
still be targets...
Will you protect
her for me...?
Will you keep her safe?
No matter where she is
or what she's doing...
swear to me you'll
be there for her...
Please, will you
make me that promise?
For cryin' out loud.
Worst possible answer.
Yeah, he is the kinda guy
who would say something like
that without thinking...
I know I'm nobody
special or anything.
I'm not going to take
his words the wrong way.
But he makes it
really difficult...
the idiot!
[Music]
A mysterious girl introduces
herself to Accelerator,
revealing a shocking truth
and forcing him to
make a tough choice.
Next time, "Last Order."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.