I finally learned
that those books Index
is always talking about are
actually stored in her memory...
Somehow I managed to escape
from the sorcerer with Index,
but her injuries
are severe.
She says magic can
be used to heal her,
but apparently, none of
the students in this city
can use this magic stuff.
So, I decided to bring
Index to Miss Komoe
and ask her for help.
[Music]
What time is it?
I need the exact minute
in Japan Standard Time...
Also, can you please
tell me what the date is?
Today is the
twentieth of July...
and the time is now
half past eight o'clock.
You didn't look at a
clock before answering...
How can you be so certain
it is 8:30 precisely?
I couldn't have
checked a clock
because there
aren't any here.
I don't need them...
But I promise, the time
I gave you was precise.
My internal clock is accurate
down to the second...
My eating habits,
exercise rhythms,
and sleep patterns
are so regulated
that my body always
knows what time it is.
Judging by the
position of the stars
and the phase of the moon,
your estimation is correct
within a .083 margin of error.
I can therefore
confirm it...
Today is July 20th and it is
8:30 p.m. Japan Standard Time...
Is that calculation consistent
with your internal clock?
Yes... Not for very
much longer, though.
We actually just passed
the fifty-three second mark.
You're injured!
You shouldn't move!
Don't be concerned...
My body can regenerate.
The cusp of Cancer.
The hour is between eight p.m.
and twelve midnight.
The direction,
westward facing...
Invoking the
protection of Undine...
We will require the
aid of an angel.
Uh... what is it
that you're doing?
It's magic.
From this point forward,
I will need your
assistance...
I must borrow your body.
Please follow my
instructions exactly...
If you do, we will accomplish
this without injury...
Your participation in
this will be appreciated.
Why don't you lie
back down instead?
We'll wait for
the ambulance...
Let's see... I must
have bandages somewhere.
Common first-aid
will do no good...
Unfortunately,
nothing you can do
will suffice to close
my wounds completely.
Nor is there any reason to
call for additional help...
Any attempt
will be useless
unless it can heal
my injuries entirely
and restore my life force
to the necessary levels
within the next few minutes.
So... what do you
want me to do...?
I don't know
anything about magic.
I didn't think it
was real 'til now.
I deeply appreciate
your cooperation.
Now, to begin...
Tell me what that is...
The black item over there.
It's a memory card.
You haven't
seen one before?
It will do. Please place it in
the center of the coffee table.
It's really more
of a tea table.
What's this...?
It looks like you've built
a miniature of the room.
The materials used
are irrelevant.
What is important is to
recreate the placement of items
as they appear in the room.
What are those?
They represent
the beer cans....
As we move forward,
it is vital that you
follow any instruction
I give down
to the letter.
A single misstep
could be disastrous...
A mistake as small as
a misdirected thought
could permanently damage
your nervous system...
understood?
Complete failure
would result
in the destruction of
your body and death.
I thought you should
be aware of the risks.
We will call an angel
and create a temple...
I will begin the
chanting now.
Please follow my example.
Link established.
What link?
We created a temple
on this table.
We have now established a
link between it and the room.
Whatever happens
in the room
will also happen
on the table.
And whatever
happens on the table
will also happen
in the room.
Now you must visualize!
What?!
Picture a golden angel...
It should have two wings...
and the body of a child.
See the form of a
beautiful angel!
An angel?
It won't work...
How am I supposed
to summon an angel?
Uh-oh.
You are not actually
summoning the angel itself.
Rather, as
the spellcaster,
you are using your will to
create the form of an angel.
Oh-okay.
A beautiful angel...
Incredible! I thought you said
I wasn't summoning
a real angel...
That looks real!
A form stabilization failure.
So long as the temple is
protected by the blue of Undine,
it is no matter.
We can continue
our work...
Let us chant.
A beautiful... angel...
Life force replenishment
underway...
Now confirming that mortal
peril has been avoided...
John's Pen is
returning to dormancy.
Are you sure
that you're okay?
Yes...
I just need some time
to recover my strength...
The wound is closed now,
so I should be fine.
Thank goodness...
Toma won't have
to pay for this.
Pay for it...? Like how?
It's difficult to explain,
but if I had died here,
the consequences he would've
faced might've been terrible.
It sounds like...
you're more concerned
about Kamijo
instead of your
own injuries.
I know it's strange.
After all...
I only just met him...
but still...
Explain this.
Miss Komoe is an
Academy City teacher.
She's a bona fide beer-drinking,
chain-smoking adult...
How is it that her
PJ's even fit you?
I mean, the age
difference must be huge.
It's rude to talk
down to people.
And anyway, they
don't fit that well.
The chest area is
way too tight on me.
Hey! After what I did,
you're making fun of me?
What...? I wasn't.
-I just...
-You just what? Huh?
No, it's nothing.
I am an adult,
thank you very much!
And as for you, Kamijo...!
It's time you answered
some questions.
Who is this girl to you?
My younger sister.
You are the worst liar
ever! Look at her!
She's got silver
hair and blue eyes.
You are clearly
not related to her!
-I'm so sorry!
-Tell... the... truth!
Miss Komoe...? May I please
ask a question first?
Fine.
If I do tell the
truth to you...
Are you gonna report it all to
Academy City's governing board?
Yes...
I'm not sure
what kind of trouble
you've gotten
yourself involved in,
but I can tell that
it's something serious.
And now that I
know about it,
it is my duty as a faculty
member and a responsible adult
to report it to
the authorities.
Whatever's going on,
it seems like you've gotten
in over your head, Kamijo...
How can I stand
back and do nothing
when one of my
students is in danger?
If you were a stranger,
I wouldn't hesitate to
involve you in this...
but you've already
done so much to help...
I don't want
you to get hurt.
That may have been a
fancy little speech,
but I can't just
leave it at that...
You aren't going to get out
of this that easily, you know.
Uh... where're you going?
I'm giving you
time to think...
There are a few groceries
I need from the supermarket.
You are going
to stay here...
I expect you to give
serious consideration
to what you're
going to tell me...
I'll be gone for a bit.
You should have more
than enough time...
Oh, and...
Yes ma'am?
There's always a chance I'll
get caught up in my shopping
and forget
about this...
But I still expect you
to explain yourself
once I get back...
I don't want you trying to
weasel your way out of it,
do you understand?
She's a nice person.
Are you talking
about Miss Komoe?
We should keep her from
getting further involved, huh?
That's right...
It wouldn't be safe for
her to use any more magic.
The grimoires are
really dangerous...
They're full of
unconventional ideas
that alter basic
laws of nature.
It's like there are
two different worlds:
this one and the one
within the grimoires.
And the other
one is toxic.
Like... poison?
When people of this world
who aren't sorcerers
read what is written
in the grimoires,
it damages their brains.
Normal humans
were never meant
to read such poisonous
ideas, you see.
That's horrible...
Is that what magic is?
It sounds evil.
You wanna know?
You want me to tell
you about it...?
The poison I carry?
You look so serious...
Hands clasped
and head bowed,
almost like you're
talking to a priest.
Yeah, you're right...
It kinda feels like you're
taking my confession.
There used to be only
one church of the cross.
Do you know why there are
so many divisions of it now?
Hmm...
Let me think...
People began to mix their
politics with religion...
When that happened,
the church fractured
into separate factions,
each one wanting to
follow a different path...
Even though they all
still shared a common God.
Each group evolved
in its own way,
developing a character
suited to its beliefs.
Character. Sure.
I belong to a branch of
the English Puritan Church.
England is a
country of magic,
so anti-sorcery practices like
witch hunts and inquisitions
became increasingly commonplace
over the centuries.
The English Puritan Church
created a special
branch for such things.
This branch
investigates magic
and develops countermeasures
against sorcerers...
It's called the Church
of Necessary Evil,
or Necessarius.
And you're part
of this sect?
You see... understanding
an impure enemy that way
taints the mind,
just as coming
into contact
with the unclean
taints the body...
but still... we continue to
stand against this impurity...
the epitome of which...
...is the library you carry
around in your head.
A piece of magic is a lot
like a formula in some ways...
If you understand its
components well enough,
you can figure out
how to neutralize
your opponent's attack.
That means that
if you understand
all the magic
in the world,
you should be able to neutralize
the power entirely...
That's why I memorized
the grimoires.
Why they were
drilled into you.
Okay...
If they're as
dangerous as you say,
you could just burn them
without reading them... right?
It's not the
books that matter.
It's what's written
inside them.
Even if the original
works were destroyed,
their contents could've
been passed on...
Besides, humans
wouldn't be able
to dispose of
the originals.
Destroying that
kind of magic
isn't something the
human mind can bear...
And since the information
can't be destroyed,
they had no choice but
to seal it in a safe place.
So, basically...
It's like there's a
bomb inside your head
and some evil people want
to get their hands on it.
Anyone who could use all
one-hundred-and-three-thousand
volumes
would have the power
to warp the entire world.
How could you?
This is major stuff,
and you waited until
now to tell me?!
You're such a skeptic
I didn't think you were
going to believe me,
and I didn't want to
frighten you off...
and also...
well... I didn't want
you to stop liking me.
That's why you
kept it from me?!
Well I deserve better!
Church of Necessary Evil?!
Magic robes?!
A whole library
of evil books?!
Yeah, it is a crazy story,
and I still have a
hard time buying it...
But that's it, right...?
No more surprises?
You owe me an apology.
Did you actually think
I wouldn't like you
just because you happened to
memorize a bunch of old books?
You just assumed I was
that petty and shallow...?
Don't leap straight
into judgment.
Have some faith!
Cheer up... Sorcerers
are no match for me.
Not while I've got
this right hand.
Except... didn't you say
they're making you take
remedial classes at school?
Did I say that?
You certainly did.
Well, forget about it.
It doesn't matter.
If it doesn't matter...
then why did you say anything
about it in the first place?
Was that just an excuse?
Did you want to
get away from me?
Am I cramping your style?
Well, are you
gonna answer me?
How is Index?
Still alive.
I've been looking into
the identity of that boy
she's got with her.
Good... Did you find out
anything about his hand?
Whatever he is...
he certainly doesn't
appear to be an esper...
or a sorcerer.
So, what, then...?
I hope you're not
trying to convince me
he's just an ordinary
high-school student.
There's no way...
A rank amateur with no power at
all repelling Innocentius...?
Not in this life time...
He's not a normal kid.
Normal...? No...
In fact, he is distinctly below
average--by all appearances,
a hopeless student who's
quick to get into a fight.
He must be concealing his
true status somehow...
..Right?
But there's something
troubling me even more...
Index was healed
using magic...
what do you think?
Is there another
magic cabal
we don't know of here
in the Far East?
If they were operating
out of the Academy City
the governing board would've
picked up on them by now.
Even so we wouldn't
know their number...
plus we don't have
any reinforcements.
She's happy, huh?
She really seems to
be having fun here.
She always makes the
best of what she has.
I wonder...
How much longer are
we going to have
to keep tearing that apart?
You're starting to
get sentimental...
You wouldn't be having
second thoughts, would you?
I know what
needs to be done.
Eventually, Miss Komoe
returned from her shopping...
She invited us to
stay at her place,
and she didn't say a word about
our earlier conversation.
Maybe she got distracted
with her errands
and forgot about it...
Or maybe she just
pretended to forget...
I wasn't about to ask.
Bath time...! Bath time!
I love bath time!
Bath time...!
I... love... bath time!
Toma! Toma!
Toma! Toma! Toma!
It's nothing...!
I just thought it was funny to
say your name a bunch of times
for no good reason.
Now that I think
about it...
there is something
I wanna ask you.
Something Komoe told me.
Listen, this is
very important.
Japanese bathhouses have
something called coffee milk.
Do this...
Then this...
And then with your
hand on your hip,
you drink it all!
I've never heard of something
called coffee milk...
Is it like a latte
or cappuccino?
You won't find anything as fancy
as that in a bathhouse...
but don't be too
disappointed.
I bet you'll get a kick
out of the bathtubs;
they're gigantic!
In England you mostly have
tight, narrow tubs, don't you?
Actually, I have no
idea what they're like.
You don't? Why?
Well, because...
the first memory I have
is of being here...
I don't really know much about
what life is like in England.
I was wondering how you
seemed to fit in so easily here.
I don't think you
understand what I mean.
I'm not from here
I'm European.
I was born in
England--London, actually
apparently I was raised
in St. George's Cathedral.
I only arrived in
Japan about a year ago,
or so I'm told, anyway.
So you're told?
Uh-huh...
Apparently I lost
my memory somehow.
It was strange...
When I first
opened my eyes,
I didn't even
know who I was.
I couldn't remember
what I'd eaten for dinner
the day before...
but I still knew all about
sorcerers, the grimoires,
Necessarius...
all that knowledge just
spinning around in my head.
It was really scary.
So you're telling me that
you lost your memory
and you have no idea
how it happened?
That's crazy!
Yeah.
What is it?
Are you angry again?
No, I'm not angry.
You sure...? If I've done
something wrong, say so...
Really...!
You shouldn't
act so immature...
It isn't attractive.
You're just about the
last person in the world
who should be lecturing
me about immaturity...
little girl.
Hey... Who're you
calling "little?"
I'm serious.
You really look angry...
Or is it just that annoying
thing you like to do
where you get all upset
because you know
it'll get under my skin?
That's one of the things
I don't like about you.
Oh, come on...
Are you really gonna
give me that crap
when you never liked
me to begin with...?
This isn't some
romantic comedy
where the two main characters
start off hating each other
until... suddenly...
Index? What's with
the puppy-dog eyes?
I was just joking
around with you...
Okay?
Toma...
You... suck!
Ow... Just great...
I'm covered in bite marks,
and she's off in the city
somewhere, all alone.
That's weird.
There's no one here...
What's happening?
Runes.
I engraved them
around this spot
so we could have
a little privacy.
And who the hell are you?
Kaori Kanzaki...
and I already
know who you are.
[Music]
It looks like there's
another sorcerer in town...
I wonder if she's the
one who attacked Index.
What kind of person would
do something like that?
Next time,
"Perfect Memory Ability.
"When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.