As it turns out,
our transfer student,
Hyoka Kazakiri, isn't human.
She's an anthropomorphic
manifestation
of AIM diffusion fields.
Still... what does
that matter, really?
Despite all that...
she's still our friend.
Now, now, monster,
there's no need for tears.
Crying only makes you
look more pathetic
and that much
easier to destroy!
I'm really sorry to
keep you waiting.
Don't worry...
Everything will be all right.
[Music]
Come on, you're stronger
than that, aren't you?
You can't start crying
over every little thing
that goes wrong.
Ellis!
That makes your day,
doesn't it...?
Somebody actually cares
about you, monster.
I guess there will always
be one idiot around.
I'm not the only one.
Why would you
do this for me?
Don't be ridiculous...
Why wouldn't I do it?
And I only had to say one
thing to these guys...
"My friend is in trouble.
I need to help her."
I've got something
to prove to you.
Whether you're human
or something else,
it doesn't matter.
You still have every
right to live your life.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
There is a place for you.
And there's nobody who
can take that away.
You belong here, Kazakiri!
Ellis...! Kill them all...
down to the last man!
Configuration B...!
Our top priority
is civilian safety!
Fire now!
Michael...!
Raphael...!
Gabriel...!
Uriel!
Symbols of the four
quarters of Heaven!
I call upon your
righteous power to aid me!
Hear my call and
be guided by me!
I'm scared!
Well, so far everything's
going as we expected.
Not that we had terribly
high expectations...
Hey, kid... are you
sure about this...?
Nobody will blame you
in the slightest
if you wanna to back out.
You saw it already...
You know what I can do.
I'm not backing out.
I'm the one who needs
to take care of this.
Wait, Toma...!
I don't understand
what's happening...
I'm scared... Don't go...!
What are you
planning to do?
Haven't you guessed yet?
I'm going to stop
that monster.
That's a tall order, kid...
Maybe Miss Tsukuyomi is lucky
to have you as a
student after all.
Prepare, men!
Count 5!
Now Count 3!
You can't do this...!
There's no way you'll
come through it alive!
I couldn't live with
myself if you died!
Toma!
Be careful, Kazakiri.
My right hand cancels out
any supernatural power.
It doesn't matter
if it's good or evil.
I doubt that you'd
be an exception.
Count 1!
We may not be able to
hold hands or anything...
but that doesn't change the fact
that we're friends, does it?
I promise you,
I'll come back alive.
You got that...?
I swear it.
You'll survive this?
Really?
Yeah...
We'll track down Index,
and the three of us will
have some fun together.
Count 0!
Ellis!
Fire!
Now then...
What are you playing at...?
You're trapped.
How're you going
to run away now?
I don't need to run away.
Do you hear me?
I don't need to run away!
I'm tired of your ranting.
Shut up!
Now to deal
with this thing.
You're gonna make
a second monster?
Unfortunately, sustaining two
at once exceeds my powers.
However... if I play
my hand correctly
there is something I can
do to get out of this mess.
Cease fire immediately!
Damn... she got away.
What is she up to?
Her target was right
in front of her,
and she gave
up that easily?
I'm overlooking
something...
What was it she told me?
That's Index's church...
Why would one of their members
do something like this?
Simple. Because I
want to start a war...
and this will be
what begins it.
So, for maximum impact,
I want to make
sure everyone knows
that I'm one of
the Church's pawns.
Now, what was that
brat's name, again?
Oh, well...
It's not as if she's
the only one I can kill.
I do have options...
I'll be happy to take
time out of my day
to kill you instead.
She's after Index!
Sure is hot out here.
Sure is.
Look at you.
What's with that crazy
outfit you've got on...?
I can't believe you're
wearing something like that
when it's this hot out.
I don't think there's anything
wrong with my clothes.
Thanks to some recent
modifications,
they're rather breezy.
Okay.
That's why...
It's all held together
with safety pins.
Impressive. How did this
get so thoroughly ripped up?
I find that memory
very distressing...
I'd appreciate it if we could
avoid the subject entirely.
I wonder why this
is taking so long.
I can't be sure,
but it sort of seemed
like the sorcerer was targeting
Hyoka in particular...
and I'm almost certain
the forms she was using
were of the London style...
I sure hope nothing bad
has happened to Hyoka.
The other girl who
was with you guys?
Is that her name, Hyoka?
Yeah...
Oh... and in this case,
Toma wasn't the one
who got her involved...
I actually introduced
him to her.
This time, eh?
How... interesting.
Ooh, I'm really
starting to get worried.
My poor friend is
trapped down there
with a terrorist
sorcerer on the loose,
and what's worse, she's
with Toma in a dimly-lit area.
With conditions like that,
any number of
things could happen,
Not that I'm
concerned about it,
but aren't you worried
about Toma's safety at all?
Huh...? Who, Toma...?
I'm not worried
about him...
No matter what
happens down there,
I know Toma will make it
back home in one piece.
What does she mean
"make it back home?"
Don't tell me he
and this girl are...
Ah...! Sphinxy,
come back here!
It'll be okay...
Although, if it's
all the same to you,
I think I'll just wait here.
You go ahead and catch
your cat and then come back.
Cats don't care for me.
I tend to rub them
the wrong way...
I would only make
things worse.
Sorry about this.
I'll track him down
as quickly as I can...
Sphinx...! Hold on!
Wait for Mommy!
Why haven't the barriers
been lifted yet?!
We don't control them.
The mall's administration
isn't our jurisdiction.
It's still going to take a
little while longer for us
to get them unlocked.
Damn!
Um... Toma...
I wanna thank you...
You know, for what
you did back there.
Sure thing...
Never mind that, though.
How are you
holding up so far?
Oh... I'm fine...
I think.
For the most part I feel
pretty normal except...
Is that giant
stone creature
going to come
after us again?
I don't think that sorcerer
was actually running away...
My guess is she escaped
so she could go
after her next target.
Her objective here
is not to kill
either one of us
specifically...
Someone else will do as long
as they meet certain criteria.
Somebody else?
Yeah...
she has options
to choose from...
and Index is one.
Oh, no...!
If that's the case,
shouldn't we tell these people?
They can do something
to protect her!
Index is not an
Academy City resident...
Antiskill can't
know about her...
If they find her,
she could be arrested.
We can only turn to
them as a last resort.
Anyway...
if I'm gonna get out,
it'll be through there...
Damn.
If they would just
lift the barriers,
I could easily get
a head start on her.
I hate that I'm already
so far behind her.
How am I gonna get down?
Uh... hold on.
Are you really going after
that woman by yourself?
Index is in danger.
No, it's okay...
I mean...
it doesn't have
to be you......
There's another way
we can help Index.
What are you
talking about?
To fight a monster...
you should send a monster,
don't you think?
It's not much...
I know it's not likely
that I'll be able to
defeat that giant...
but at the very least
I can act as a decoy.
If that thing
comes after me,
it should give Index
the chance to get away.
I know that's not
a lot to offer...
but what more can you
expect from a monster?
Please... are you still
going on about that?
Get it through your head:
you're no monster...
Is that how you
think I see you...?
As some thing to
be thrown away?!
It's for the best...
I know it is!
I'm okay with
being a monster...
It's because I'm a monster
that I didn't die,
even after everything that
stone creature did to me.
And it's because
I'm a monster
that I'm able to stand
up to that giant
and take another
beating if I have to.
I will do it.
I will protect the people
I care about, no matter what.
That's why I've made
peace with it all...
That's why I'm actually
glad to be a monster.
Wha...!
Kazakiri!!
I knew it...
I'm okay.
This is me.
I'm Hyoka.
There's nothing of
substance here,
nothing solid.
It's all made from the
AIM diffusion fields
constantly emitted
by the espers.
An ephemeral city.
An unseen place that exists
in the same location...
as Academy City.
I was afraid of the
role I had to play here
in this illusionary town.
I would determine
somebody's place in life...
just by looking at them.
I would turn their
world upside down...
with no more than
a single thought.
I was the spring that
powered the mechanism.
My job was to breathe life
into the gigantic wind-up
machine that is society...
to make the
world go 'round.
I couldn't go outside.
I could look from the
shadow city and see things
and people in the
outside world,
but I couldn't touch
anything or talk to anyone.
But then...
something changed.
For the first time, I went
into the outside world.
Excuse me...
It's simple...
just push the button.
Today, for the first
time, I spoke...
For the first time,
I put on real clothes...
a boy saw me undressed.
For the first time,
I went to an arcade...
where a boy saw me
undressed again.
Today... for the first time...
I made friends.
When she finds out
what I truly am,
that I'm a monster...
Index may not want to
be my friend anymore.
But even so...
I'll save her.
I will!
There you are,
little rascal!
If you don't stop
being so difficult,
you're going to be in a
heap of trouble, young man!
Come on... we have to go
back to the loudmouth...
You behave.
That sounds like...
like footsteps?!
Basic theory
from Kabbalah.
Originated in the
sixteenth century...
Primary application is defense
and the elimination
of hostiles.
English Puritan formula
combined with the original...
Linguistic derivation
changed from Hebrew to English.
Judging by formulaic
construct...
remote controlled.
And in that case...
TTTR!
CFA.
PIOBTLL
I'm not able to use magic
to fight against it...
but I am able to
disrupt the spell a bit.
"Spell Intercept"...
Using imposition chants to
cut off the caster's control.
CR, BBF, TTNATWITOD
Manipulating him
isn't enough.
His self-repair operations
run in cycles...
I'll backtrack them.
Wait for an opening.
Right there!
This might work.
CR...
MBFPADCOG!
This isn't good...
He switched from
remote to self-control.
I can't intercept anymore!
Toma...
[Music]
Things are becoming more
and more complicated.
But no matter
what happens...
one thing is certain.
Next time "Imaginary
Number School District
Five-Element Agency."
When science and
magic cross paths,
a story is born.