At a beach resort away
from Academy City,
I was reunited with my
parents and little cousin.
There, we fell victim to
the effects of a spell
called Angel Fall.
A member of the Russian
Orthodox Church showed up,
along with a woman
named Kanzaki,
and, strangely enough,
my friend Tsuchimikado.
As it turns out, he's a
member of Necessarius...
Wait, what?!
[Music]
It's a simple
explanation, really.
You see, Kami...
I'm a member of
Necessarius, too.
Necessarius...?
Then, you're a...
Yeah... I'm a sorcerer.
But...
But it's impossible for
a sorcerer to live in
Academy City, right...?
Think about it for a minute,
and you'll see, Kami.
Science and magic
are enemies, yes...?
A little bit of espionage
between two rival sides
is hardly surprising...
A double agent
can be very useful.
And that's what you are?
Yes, basically,
I'm a spy...
I know pretty much everything
about you, Kami...
Including, of course, your
Imagine Breaker and its power.
But... my job as a spy
comes with a price.
Since I've taken so much
of the esper curriculum,
I can't use my
magic anymore.
At any rate, there's
a good chance that
whoever it was that put
Angel Fall into motion
has gotten close to you
somehow...
The ritual site is
tied to you as well...
We're all going to need to work
together for a little while.
Hopefully then
we can determine
the caster's
purpose and plans.
Misha Kruezhev,
what do you say?
Any objections?
Observation one...
Your suggestion is the
smartest course of action
we can take.
Hey...! I think I should
have a say in this.
I'm with my
family right now,
and I haven't seen them
in a long time...
My parents and my cousin are
staying with me at the inn.
A family reunion,
how touching;
but tell me, do your
parents and cousin
look like they're
supposed to?
My rotten luck.
Good luck charm,
yeah right.
Just a cheap
useless trinket.
The god's power dwells
within replicas.
Or at least, that's what people
who worship idols believe.
I can't believe
you're a sorcerer.
That's not exactly
true, though...
I was a sorcerer.
I was once the most
highly respected
feng shui specialist
in all of Necessarius,
but now I'm just another
ordinary person.
Aren't you going to go in there
and visit with the others?
Nope I couldn't even
if I wanted to...
When Angel Fall first
went into effect,
Kanzaki and I
put up a barrier
as soon as we realized
what was happening,
but we weren't able
to avoid it entirely.
Judging by the reactions
I've been getting,
I have the rather
dubious luck
of looking like
Hitotsui Hajime.
Wait, I think I
know that name.
You mean that celebrity
guy with the hair?
So who does
Kanzaki look like?
Interesting...
looks like our Toma has
made some unique friends
while he's been
away at school.
I'll say! You're
totally cool, mister!
With your bright red hair and
that cigarette in your mouth.
Is that a barcode tattooed
on your cheek...?
What's the word
I'm looking for?
It's so...
I think you're trying
to say it's rad,
right, Aunt Shina?
-Yes, that's it.
-Oh, ... right...
almost forgot.
I have some Egyptian
good luck charms here.
Geez...! Enough already
with the souvenirs,
Uncle Toya.
All right, back
to our guest...
What did you say
your name was?
It's Kaori Kanzaki.
She looks like Stiyl?!
That's too funny.
Hold on, didn't
you just say
that you and Kanzaki
raised a barrier...?
I thought espers weren't
able to use magic at all.
They shouldn't...
This is the kind of thing
that happens when we do.
I used my magic one more time,
and my blood vessels
burst... Boom! .
It's going to be
the death of me.
Can I ask you
for a favor...?
You know how you're always
moaning about your rotten luck?
It would be best if you
could avoid doing that
in front of Kanzaki.
With her, it's not bad
luck that's the problem...
It's her own good luck that
she can't stand thinking about.
Since when is good
luck a problem?
There is an organization
in Japan called Amakusa--
a secret order of warriors
within the Catholic Church...
Kanzaki was set up as the
organization's top priestess...
She was born into
the position.
They said it
was her destiny.
She's a saint and
a stigma-user...
one of only a handful
in the world...
You know what a
saint is, right...?
A human who carries the power
of God inside of them.
When she releases
her stigma,
she can call
upon that power,
and for a short time,
she has abilities beyond
any normal human...
She can't stand that her
good luck came to her
because she happened to be
born under a fortunate star.
Must it always come back
to God with you people...?
So... why does an accident of
birth bother her so much?
I guess that's one
thing only Kanzaki
can ever know for sure...
Just think about
it, though...
How would it feel
to be so blessed?
To be lucky in every
single thing you do?
It's like her life is one
big lottery drawing...
She always wins...
which means she has to watch as
everybody around her loses.
I can't put up with
this any longer.
As it happens, I... Well...
Angel Fall has made
me look like...
I heard about it...
They all think you
look like Stiyl.
Unfortunately.... I'd
like to take a bath
to get the soreness
out of my muscles,
but if I used the women's
baths and someone came in,
there'd be a big scene.
And you wouldn't
be comfortable
using the men's baths if
anyone else came in, either.
Exactly. Which is
why I'd like you
to stand watch out here...
Make sure that
nobody else comes in.
Do you understand?
I'm counting on you, Toma.
Just my luck.
Oh, right. I need to be careful
not to say that around Kanzaki.
Toma... so this is
where you ran off to.
-Oh, Dad.
-This works out perfectly.
What do you say we take
a nice father-son
steam together for
old times' sake?
No, wait, hold on...!
We can't right now.
There's someone in there.
Yeah, so what
if there is...?
This is a hot spring,
that's kind of what
you would expect.
Well, uh, you
see, it's just....
You're acting so
strangely today.
Come on, we're both men.
What is there to be
embarrassed about?
-I'm really sorry.
-Oh, hey...
if it isn't the
cool, red-headed,
cigarette-smoking,
tattooed Kanzaki!
How's it goin'?
Useless.
You'd toss aside
all you owe him over
nothing more than
a little nudity?
Or have you already
forgotten that Kami saved
Index's life when
no one else could...?
Is seeing you naked a
big deal compared to that?
You should show him
a bit more gratitude.
I haven't forgotten how
much I owe him, but...
I don't think you
would understand.
Man, you've got some
really weird friends,
you know that, son...?
Why was that guy
so touchy about
sharing the steam
baths with other men?
Oh, that's kind
of a long story.
Oh, really...? I think I
know what you're getting at.
He plays for the other
team, doesn't he?
Well that's okay
in this day and age
it's nothing to
be embarrassed about.
Now you're letting your
imagination run away with you...
It's not like that, Dad.
That's right...
If everyone's
appearance is different
because of Angel Fall...
then this might not be what
my dad really looks like.
He could be someone
else entirely.
Hey, Toma... is something
bothering you?
You're so quiet.
Don't worry, Dad.
It's nothing.
Heh... that look reminds
me of your mother.
A long time ago...
before we got married and
were still just dating...
the time would come to say
goodbye for the night...
your mother would get that
exact look on her face...
It was difficult for me
to see her like that.
But at the same
time, it was sweet.
You take after your mother
when it comes to looks.
Oh, yeah! I forgot I
have this souvenir
to give you from Mexico.
I don't want it, Dad!
Is that Misha?
Yeah, it is.
What a pity...
for such a young
and innocent girl
to be so troubled
by something...
It almost seems like
she came here hoping
someone would offer
their help...
Good luck, son... I
know you can do it.
Where are you--?
Thanks a lot.
What are you
up to out here?
Uh... I can stay here with
you if you're homesick.
I was on my way back in, but
I'm not rushin' or anything.
That was the worst
pun ever...!
Maybe if I'm lucky she'll
think I was just talking
and not trying to
make a joke.
Want some?
Have you been able to
find out anything
new about Angel Fall?
Okay.
It's not like I know a whole
lot about this angel stuff...
but what's the
caster's goal?
Why would they wanna put a
spell like Angel Fall into play?
Possible reason one...
to gain for themselves
the incredible power
an angel possesses...
or perhaps to
elevate themselves
from human to the
rank of angel.
For the moment, Angel
Fall is incomplete.
Okay, but what
does that mean?
The power of an angel is
great enough that with it,
a single person could
bring down the Vatican.
Angel Fall is a
serious threat.
Once complete...
the chaos it unleashes
could destroy the world.
We must discover the
caster's identity quickly.
If they complete
the spell,
we will all be doomed.
I guess this is a bad
time to be standing around
chewing gum if it's
that serious...
I'm sorry.
The whole world
is in danger?
What has gotten
into you, Toya?
I can't remember the last
time you were so energetic!
It's like you're
twenty again.
What's the
special occasion?
It's from spending
time with Toma today...
It reminded me
of the past.
Besides... he
always said
he wanted a younger
brother or sister someday.
Oh, my, maybe we
should give him one.
Sorry about this, Misha...
I've got a more
urgent crisis
than the end of the
world on my hands.
Stop right now...!
Stop it! Stop it!
Ah! Toma...! It's
not a good time.
Oh, my, how sweet...
Toma's been away
from us so long
that he wants to sleep
together as a family...
We'll all snuggle
up in bed just like
when he was a little boy.
Oh no...! Oh no...!
What's happened?
Toma isn't in our room...!
It doesn't look like he's been
back at all since last night.
Where are you, Toma?
Oh dear, oh dear!
This is terrible.
What's the matter,
sweetheart?
Why's everyone
making so much noise?
It's too early for this.
Toma...!
What's the rush? This is
supposed to be a vacation.
I just realized I forgot
to lock the front door
when we left...
I'm going to go back
and take care of it.
But that's going to take
you most of the day.
It's a pretty
long train ride.
It'll be all right. I should
be back by this evening.
Question one:
Would it be a problem for
me to accompany you?
But why?
I will repeat
question one...
Would it be a problem
for me to accompany you?
That would be lovely...
I never enjoy
traveling alone.
With you along, I'll
have someone to talk to.
Come on, Misha...
We'll have a wonderful
time together.
Why would Misha want to go
with Ind--I mean, with Mom?
I knew this would
happen, Toma.
You two must have had
quite a special time
together last night.
You must know
what she's doing.
It's the oldest
trick in the book.
She'll get friendly
with your mom
and before you know it,
What the hell are
you talking about?
That's ridiculous.
You certainly seemed to be
enjoying her company last night.
What? Wait just a minute
were you spying on us,
you dirty old pervert...?
Well, if you were, then you
should know nothing happened.
Calm down, I'm just
joking with you...
but you know, son...
it's rare to find a girl who's
that refined nowadays...
So shy and delicate,
she wouldn't even
hold your hand
when you
gave it to her.
Oh... yeah.
My right hand.
She wouldn't touch it.
For the moment, Angel
Fall is incomplete.
Once complete...
the chaos it unleashes
could destroy the world.
Misha really said that?
Yes, she did...
We're not really
clear on the story
behind Angel Fall, right?
It seems like there are
a lot of gaps to fill in.
That's right.
It's a previously
unknown phenomenon.
We've looked everywhere,
but not even the British
Library has anything.
Suppose the caster hasn't
completed the spell...
If that's true...
how would Misha know?
She also said that the spell
would destroy the world...
If it's that unknown,
how can she be sure?
Plus, I would like to
know why she refused
to touch my right hand...
Is it just because she's
incredibly shy...?
Or something else?
So she's the one
who's behind all this.
She doesn't want to
neutralize Angel Fall
while it's in progress.
I think she wants
it to be completed.
Kami... take us to the house.
Right!
Hmm...? You want a
map to the house?
You guys moved, right...?
I need to know the way
to get to the new house.
Why the sudden
interest to see it...?
Your mom will be fine.
You don't need
to go after her.
Wait a minute, I
think I get it now.
There's nothing to get!
It's not your mother you
wanna go running after,
it's that
pretty little Misha--
I've already told you,
there's nothing going on!
-Now hurry!
-All right, all right. Here.
Let's just assume Misha is the
one moving Angel Fall along...
Why would she
go with Index...
I mean my mom.
Why go with her?
No idea... It doesn't
make any sense to me.
To find out, we'll have
to ask Misha personally.
So this is it...
my family's new house.
You here, Mom...? Misha?
The train does
take longer.
We'll have to wait
here until they arrive.
Hey, Kami, look!
Geez...
My old man sure is a
hardcore souvenir collector.
In here, too.
That's my name...
I drew that...?
Nope, nothing... I don't
remember making it.
What's up?
You look troubled.
So it's here.
I never would have expected
something like that.
Is there something
wrong with these?
Don't touch them!
Hey, what's going
on, Tsuchimikado?!
Spit it out, will you?
That's her.
That's my mother.
Huh? Dad?
It's us from
last New Year's.
See, that's you and me.
Do you remember me now...?
Please, say you do.
He's the same here......
and here, too.
That means my father...
wasn't affected
by the spell.
What does this mean?
Explain it to me.
Angel Fall
doesn't affect you
because of Imagine Breaker.
Aside from that,
there is only one person
who wouldn't be
touched by it.
And that's the person
who is responsible
for casting the spell.
Oh dear, oh dear!
I can't believe
I did that...
How silly of me!
Ah...! It's
Hitotsui Hajime!
I have no idea
what you're doing here,
but I don't care...!
I have to tell you...
I'm one of your
absolute biggest fans!
Go, Kami... Now!
Have you forgotten what
Misha was going to do
when she thought you
were the caster?
How is this possible, Dad?
How could you be
responsible for this?
And what are you doing
getting yourself
involved with the occult?
Hey, watch where
you're going!
You got a death wish?
Uh... Himegami...?
Get outta the way, kid...
Move or I run you
over, ya got me?
Hey... what're you doing?
Please just give me
a ride. I'm begging you!
What the hell?
Does it look like I'm
running a taxi service here?
This is important...
It's my father. I think
his life is in danger!
What?
If I don't get to him,
he'll die...!
I have to save
him somehow.
Please help me!
Oh man! You sure
know how to tug at
a guy's heartstrings,
don't you...?
Such a good, dutiful
son in this day and age!
All right!
You better get that
seatbelt fastened on tight...
I won't take the blame
if you go flying.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on...!
Move it, move it,
move it, move it!
-Where is Misha?
-Where's my father...?
I need to find
my dad right now...
and Misha, too.
That's what I wanted
to ask you about.
You were the one
chasing after her...
As for Mr. oya,
he's at the beach...
What exactly is going on?
I see.
I want you to remain
here for the moment.
Given what you've told
me, this is my task now...
I will take
Mr. oya into my--
Not happening.
I'm going to take
care of this, not you.
-But, Toma
-"But" nothing, Kanzaki!
Don't you see? Toya
Kamijo is my father!
He's the only
dad I have...
This is up to me.
Dad...
[Music]
When a being that transcends
human understanding appears,
Kanzaki steps forward
to keep it from
destroying the world...
As for Tsuchimikado...
Next time,
"The Power of God."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.