&gt;&gt; BUT NOW, IF THIS IS HOW IT
IS, I WISH YOU'D KEPT ON BEING A
JERK TO ME.
[ CRYING ]
IF YOU HAD, I WOULDN'T HAVE
REALIZED HOW I FELT ABOUT YOU.
I WOULDN'T HAVE FELT SAD AND
JEALOUS WHEN I FOUND OUT ABOUT
HER, AND I WOULDN'T HAVE TRIED
FORGETTING ABOUT YOU AND FALLING
IN LOVE WITH KIRITO INSTEAD!
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY.
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERS ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
GO ON.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
>>I REMEMBER THE DAY WHEN
EVERYTHING CHANGED -- THE DAY I
FOUND OUT I WASN'T REALLY PART
OF THIS FAMILY.
IT FELT WEIRD, LIKE I DIDN'T
FIT IN WITH THEM ANYMORE.
AND I FOUND THIS OUT WHEN I WAS
10.
[ SUGUHA SHOUTING IN DISTANCE ]
I'D WONDER, "WHO IS SHE?" AND
"DO I REALLY KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT HER?"
MAYBE THAT FEELING I HAD OF NOT
FITTING IN WAS THE THING THAT
DROVE ME TO ONLINE GAMING.
I GUESS I FIGURED IN THE
VIRTUAL WORLD, NO ONE KNOWS
ANYTHING ABOUT ANYONE, SO I
DOVE RIGHT IN AND THOUGHT IT
WAS WHERE I BELONGED.
BUT THOSE TWO YEARS I SPENT
TRAPPED IN S.A.O. TAUGHT ME
SOMETHING.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A REAL
AND A VIRTUAL WORLD IS SLIM AT
BEST.
IT'S A WASTE OF TIME ASKING
PEOPLE WHO THEY REALLY ARE.
ALL YOU CAN DO IS ACCEPT THEM
AS IS AND HAVE FAITH IN THEM,
'CAUSE, IN THE END, WHOEVER YOU
THINK THEY ARE -- THAT'S WHO
THEY REALLY ARE.
WHEN I GOT BACK TO THE REAL
WORLD AND SAW SUGUHA'S FACE, I
WAS REALLY, TRULY HAPPY.
RIGHT THEN AND THERE, I SWORE
I'D DO WHATEVER I COULD TO TRY
TO CLOSE THE GAP THAT HAD GROWN
BETWEEN US OVER THE LAST COUPLE
OF YEARS.
BUT HOW DO I DO THAT?
WHAT CAN I DO FOR SUGU?
SUGU, I'LL WAIT FOR YOU IN ARUN,
ON THE NORTH TERRACE.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
&gt;&gt; [ CRYING ]
HOW COULD I BE SO HORRIBLE TO
YOU, AND HOW COULD YOU BE SO
STRONG?
I WISH I COULD BE AS STRONG AS
YOU, BIG BROTHER.
I TOLD YOU TO HANG IN THERE, TO
NOT GIVE UP ON THE ONE YOU LOVE,
BUT I CAN'T DO THAT.
AND NOW I CAN'T STOP CRYING.
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
I GUESS THIS IS HOW IT IS.
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; LEAFA?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; UH, HI.
Y-YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
&gt;&gt; WAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT THE SALAMANDERS CAUGHT
YOU.
&gt;&gt; YEAH. WELL, I SORT OF
POISONED THEM ALL AND ESCAPED.
&gt;&gt; NO WAY. YOU POISONED THEM?
&gt;&gt; BIG-TIME, AND AFTER I GOT
AWAY, I TRACKED YOU HERE.
HANG ON.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ALONE?
WHERE'S THAT SPRIGGAN?
&gt;&gt; OH, YEAH.
WELL...
I KIND OF...SAID SOMETHING
REALLY MEAN TO HIM.
IT WASN'T COOL, AND I SHOULDN'T
HAVE SAID IT.
IT WAS...PRETTY STUPID OF ME.
[ SNIFFLES ]
OH, NEVER MIND.
I'M JUST BEING WEIRD.
I'M NOT GONNA BE SEEING HIM
AROUND ANYMORE.
COME ON.
LET'S GO BACK TO SYLVAIN.
&gt;&gt; DON'T CRY LIKE THAT.
WAIT!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU SHOULDN'T BE CRYING LIKE
THAT!
&gt;&gt; UH, SORRY?
&gt;&gt; THE LEAFA I KNOW IS ALWAYS
SMILING AND HAPPY, AND I --
WELL, I'D NEVER LEAVE YOU LIKE
THAT!
I'D STAY WITH YOU ALWAYS, IN
HERE AND IN THE REAL WORLD!
I-I, UH -- LEAFA -- I MEAN,
SUGUHA -- I LOVE YOU!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] YOU WHAT?
WAIT. DON'T DO THAT.
NO! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
&gt;&gt; AAAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; UH...OH.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; UH, ARE YOU OKAY?
&gt;&gt; OHH, WHERE DID I GO WRONG?
AFTER EVERYTHING I'VE SAID AND
DONE, I THOUGHT ALL I HAD TO DO
WAS FIND THE GUTS TO CONFESS MY
FEELINGS TO YOU.
&gt;&gt; YOU REALLY ARE A MORON,
AREN'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; [ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; EVEN SO, I COULD LEARN A
THING OR TWO FROM YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
HEY.
&gt;&gt; HERE I AM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SUGUHA --
&gt;&gt; KAZUTO, I WANT A REMATCH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; LET'S FINISH WHAT WE STARTED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AND THIS TIME, NO
HOLDING BACK.
&gt;&gt; NOW I KNOW WHY HE LOOKED SO
COMPOSED.
HERE I COME!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> WHAT ARE YOUDOING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
LOOK...
I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE, BUT I
JUST DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO GO ABOUT
DOING IT...
SO, I WAS GONNA THROW THE DUEL.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
YOU WERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M SORRY.
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THINK MY PROBLEM IS
I NEVER REALLY CAME BACK TO THE
REAL WORLD AFTER S.A.O., AND I
CAN'T COME BACK UNTIL SHE WAKES
IN A WAY, THE GAME HASN'T ENDED
FOR ME YET.
AND I GUESS THAT'S WHY I STILL
HAVEN'T FIGURED OUT HOW I FIT IN
AT HOME OR WITH YOU -- NOT YET,
ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; MM.
AND WHEN YOU DO, I'LL BE THERE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW LONG IT
TAKES.
I'LL BE WAITING FOR THE DAY YOU
COME BACK TO US FOR REAL.
UNTIL THEN...I'LL HELP YOU IN
HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; SO, UH...WAIT.
WHAT'S GOING ON AGAIN?
&gt;&gt; THREE PLAYERS ARE GONNA RAID
THE WORLD TREE TODAY.
HE'S PLAYER 1, YOU'RE PLAYER 2,
AND YOURS TRULY MAKES 3.
&gt;&gt; OH. OKAY.
WAIT. WHAT?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI, YOU THERE?
&gt;&gt; HI, DADDY.
WHAT IS IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I NEED SOME INFO ON
THE GUARDIANS.
YOU LEARN ANYTHING?
&gt;&gt; THE STATS FOR ONE AREN'T VERY
HIGH, BUT THAT'S NOT THE
PROBLEM.
THERE'S JUST TOO MANY OF THEM.
AS I SEE IT, THIS QUEST WAS
DESIGNED TO BE NEXT TO
IMPOSSIBLE TO FINISH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING IS THEY ALL ADD UP TO ONE
UNBEATABLE BOSS, HUH?
&gt;&gt; YES, BUT DON'T FORGET YOUR
SKILLS AND XP ARE REALLY HIGH,
SO MAYBE, WITH A BURST OF SPEED,
YOU CAN SMASH RIGHT THROUGH
THEM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM-HMM.
HEY, GUYS...
THIS ISN'T YOUR FIGHT.
THE ONLY WAY I'M GONNA GET
THROUGH IS WITH YOUR HELP.
BUT TIME'S RUNNING OUT, SO WE
HAVE TO GO NOW.
&gt;&gt; DON'T WORRY.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN TO GET
YOU UP THERE.
YOU READY?
LET'S SEE THAT GAME FACE.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
WELL, I GUESS I DON'T HAVE A
CHOICE, SINCE WE WERE DESTINED
TO BE TOGETHER FOREVER.
&gt;&gt; OKAY! DON'T TALK STUPID.
&gt;&gt; OW! SORRY! GEEZ!
&gt;&gt; WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANKS, GUYS.
I MEAN IT.
I'LL DRAW THE GUARDIANS'
ATTENTION.
WHILE I DO, STAY BACK AND HEAL
YOU SHOULDN'T BE IN ANY DANGER
THEN.
&gt;&gt; MM.
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
LET'S GO.
[ MID-TEMPO OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING ]
&gt;&gt; Both: SOO FILLAH HAYDLE
ASTALOO PROTTOH SUPAAL BAANI!
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; THAT'S AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; THERE'S A LOT MORE COMING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM!
[ GASPS ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; NOW, RECON!
&gt;&gt; RIGHT!
[ BOTH GRUNT ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
WHY ARE THE GUARDIANS TARGETING
US INSTEAD OF HIM?
&gt;&gt; MY GUESS IS THEY'RE USING A
DIFFERENT TARGETING ALGORITHM
THAN ANY OF THE OTHER BOSSES IN
THE GAME.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GONNA BE
DOING SOME FIGHTING AFTER ALL.
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
WAIT!
&gt;&gt; WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
&gt;&gt; WAIT A SECOND.
LISTEN, I'M NOT SURE WHAT'S
GOING ON HERE, BUT, LIKE, IS
THIS RAID THAT IMPORTANT?
&gt;&gt; YEAH. YEAH, IT IS.
I DON'T THINK IT'S JUST A
GAME -- NOT NOW, ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; [ GULPS ]
[ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
THEN I'M GONNA HELP YOU HELP
THAT SPRIGGAN!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
WAIT! RECON!
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; SE-AHH MAREETA FIMM GLOWN
VIN-DOH!
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; NO! YOU IDIOT!
[ GASPS ]
HEAL!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; RECON! THAT'S ENOUGH!
GO ON! GET OUTSIDE!
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; EKKU KALLA SVALT TU-GARLI
BELFA HI-MUN!
&gt;&gt; NO WAY!
HE'S USING A DARK MAGIC SPELL!
&gt;&gt; BLOTOH LEGGIN' GARPAH!
KNEEZA FALL!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
A SELF-DESTRUCT SPELL!
HE USED IT EVEN THOUGH THE
PENALTY'S WORSE THAN A NORMAL
DEATH!
THAT DUMMY!
WHAT WAS HE THINKING?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
NO!
OH, NO.
NOW WHAT?!
HE CAN'T KEEP THIS UP!
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT ARE THE SYLPHS
DOING HERE?
&gt;&gt; NO WAY!
THEY MADE IT!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; DRAGONS.
IT'S THE CAIT SITH, AND THEY
BROUGHT THE WHOLE AR--
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; HELLO, THERE!
I HOPE WE'RE NOT LATE.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, SORRY!
IT TOOK US A WHILE TO GET READY,
BUT WE'RE HERE NOW!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
SAKUYA! ALICIA!
&gt;&gt; OKAY, DRAGOONS!
GET READY TO TOAST THESE
SUCKERS!
&gt;&gt; SYLPH WARRIORS, PREPARE TO
ENGAGE THE ENEMY!
&gt;&gt; FIRE BREATH...ATTA-A-A-A-CK!
&gt;&gt; FENRIR STORM...FIRE AT WILL!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OHH.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU!
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING!
&gt;&gt; YOU DON'T HAVE TO THANK US.
WE CAN'T EVEN BEGIN TO REPAY
THAT SPRIGGAN FOR ALL HE'S DONE.
&gt;&gt; SAKUYA'S GOT A POINT, YOU
KNOW.
I MEAN, THE ONLY REASON WE'RE
HERE FOR THIS LITTLE RAID'S
'CAUSE OF ALL THE MONEY HE GAVE
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; WARRIORS, FORWARD TO BATTLE!
[ ALL SHOUTING ]
DESTROY THEM ALL! KEEP GOING!
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
SUGU!
&gt;&gt; YEAH?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WATCH MY BACK, OKAY?!
&gt;&gt; YOU GOT IT!
&gt;&gt; FOLLOW THEIR LEAD!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; KAZUTO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; YOU CAN DO IT!
GO, KAZUTO!
G-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O-O!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
WE'RE CLEARING OUT!
EVERYONE, FALL BACK!
>>KEEP GOING.
FLY!
KEEP FLYING AS LONG AS YOU
CAN...
TO THE VERY END.
>> Kirito: DAMN IT!
[ GASPS ]
NOW WHAT DO I DO?
[ GRUNTS ]
HEY, YUI!
&gt;&gt; YES, DADDY?
DADDY, SOMETHING STRANGE IS
GOING ON.
THIS DOOR ISN'T LOCKED BY A
QUEST FLAG.
IT'S LOCKED BY THE SYSTEM
ADMINISTRATOR.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED
TO MEAN?
&gt;&gt; RESTRICTED ACCESS.
THIS DOOR WAS NEVER INTENDED TO
BE OPENED BY A PLAYER!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
NO. WAIT.
THAT'S IT!
HEY, YUI, SEE IF THIS WILL WORK.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
I'M TRANSFERRING THE CODE.
[ BEEPING ]
[ RUMBLING ]
WE'RE GONNA TELEPORT!
DADDY, GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]