[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; [ HISSES ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; EVERYONE! ATTACK!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SNARLING ]
[ WEAPON FIRING ]
[ SNARLING ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ LABORED BREATHING ]
&gt;&gt; Agil: HOW MANY DID WE LOSE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: 14 OF US DIED.
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ GASPS ]
OH, MY GOD.
[ PEOPLE GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: AND WE STILL GOT 25
FLOORS TO GO.
&gt;&gt; Agil: 25 MORE FLOORS?
HOW THE HELL ARE WE EVEN GONNA
MAKE IT THAT FAR?
[ PEOPLE WHISPERING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO!
WHAT ARE YOU --
[ PEOPLE MURMURING ]
AN "IMMORTAL OBJECT"?
COMMANDER HEATHCLIFF, W-WHAT'S
GOING ON?
>> Kirito: I THINK I GOT THE
ANSWER TO THAT.
THE REASON WHY THE COMMANDER'S
HP NEVER HITS YELLOW IS 'CAUSE
HE'S PROTECTED BY THE SYSTEM.
[ PEOPLE GASP ]
YOU KNOW, EVER SINCE DAY ONE,
SOMETHING'S ALWAYS BUGGED ME
ABOUT THIS WHOLE THING.
I WAS ALWAYS WONDERING -- "WHERE
IS HE HIDING WHILE HE WATCHES US
AND CONTROLS EVERYTHING IN THIS
WORLD?"
WELL, THE ANSWER'S PRETTY
SIMPLE.
IT'S BASIC PSYCHOLOGY.
IN FACT, IT'S SO SIMPLE, EVERY
KID KNOWS IT.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE BORING
THAN WATCHING SOMEONE ELSE PLAY
AN RPG.
IS THERE...AKIHIKO KAYABA?
[ PEOPLE GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: JUST FOR MY
CURIOSITY'S SAKE, WOULD YOU
MIND TELLING ME HOW YOU FIGURED
IT OUT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THE FIRST TIME I KNEW
SOMETHING WAS UP WAS DURING OUR
DUEL.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU TURNED THE
TABLES ON ME?
THAT MOVE WAS WAY TOO FAST.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: YES, I THOUGHT SO.
IT WAS A MISTAKE TO THINK THAT
WOULD GO UNNOTICED BY YOU.
BUT YOU WERE SO STRONG AND SO
FAST, THE ONLY CHOICE I HAD WAS
TO ENGAGE THE SYSTEM'S ASSIST
MODE.
[ PEOPLE GASP ]
YES, I AM AKIHIKO KAYABA.
AND NOW THAT MY IDENTITY'S BEEN
REVEALED, IT SHOULD COME AS NO
SURPRISE THAT I AM THE FINAL
BOSS ON THE TOP FLOOR.
[ PEOPLE GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, THE STRONGEST
PLAYER IN THE WHOLE GAME ENDS UP
BEING THE FINAL BOSS.
KIND OF CLICHé, ISN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: ACTUALLY, I KIND OF
LIKE THAT ANGLE.
ONE THING'S FOR SURE -- I ALWAYS
THOUGHT YOU'D BE THE ONE
STANDING BEFORE ME AT THE VERY
END.
YOU KNOW, DUAL-WIELDING IS A
RARE SKILL -- THE KIND THAT'S
ONLY GIVEN TO THE PLAYER WITH
THE FASTEST REACTION TIME.
HE IS THE HERO OF THIS
STORY -- THE ONE WHO RISES UP TO
CHALLENGE THE DEMON KING.
BUT YOU -- THE POWER YOU'VE
DISPLAYED EXCEEDED MY
EXPECTATIONS.
I GUESS THESE UNEXPECTED TWISTS
AND TURNS ARE WHAT MAKES MMORPGs
SO THRILLING TO PLAY.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
OUR LOYALTY...
OUR HOPE...
HOW DARE YOU?
HOW DARE YOU?!
HOW DARE YOU?!!
UNH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: PARALYSIS?
[ MACHINE BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO.
[ ALL GROANING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S THE PLAN NOW,
HUH?
YOU GONNA KILL EVERYONE HERE AND
COVER IT UP OR SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: OH, GOD, NO.
THAT WOULDN'T BE SPORTING OF ME,
NOW, WOULD IT?
NO, I HAVE A BETTER IDEA.
I'M GOING TO HEAD FOR THE TOP
FLOOR AND WAIT FOR ALL OF YOU
THERE.
I'LL BE INSIDE THE RUBY PALACE.
IT'S A SHAME I HAVE TO LEAVE YOU
ALL SO SOON.
I'VE SPENT LOTS OF TIME
DEVELOPING THE KNIGHTS OF THE
BLOOD OATH AND OTHER ELITE
PLAYERS.
OH, WELL. [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE ALL STRONG, SO I'M
SURE YOU'LL REACH ME --
EVENTUALLY.
BUT BEFORE I GO...
KIRITO, I FEEL YOU DESERVE SOME
KIND OF REWARD FOR DISCOVERING
MY IDENTITY, SO...
I'LL GIVE YOU A CHANCE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CHANCE FOR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: TO FIGHT ME
ONE-ON-ONE -- RIGHT HERE, RIGHT
NOW.
OH, AND MY IMMORTALITY WILL BE
DEACTIVATED.
DEFEAT ME AND YOU CLEAR THE
GAME, AND ALL OF THE PLAYERS
WILL BE ABLE TO LOG OUT FROM
THIS WORLD.
NO STRINGS ATTACHED.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: DON'T DO IT, KIRITO.
I DON'T LIKE IT.
WE SHOULD FALL BACK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
I HAVE TO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, THEN.
LET'S FINISH IT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T RUN AWAY IF IT MEANS
ENDING THIS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU BETTER NOT DIE.
YOU HEAR ME?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO.
I'M GONNA WIN.
I PROMISE I'M GONNA END THIS
WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY.
I BELIEVE IN YOU, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Agil: KIRITO! DON'T!
&gt;&gt; Klein: KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AGIL.
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANKS FOR SUPPORTING
ALL THE PLAYERS IN THE GAME
SINCE DAY ONE.
YEAH, I KNEW.
YOU ACT LIKE YOU'RE ALL ABOUT
THE MONEY, BUT I KNOW YOU SPENT
EVERY PENNY YOU HAD ON HELPING
THE INTERMEDIATE PLAYERS LEVEL
&gt;&gt; Agil: [ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: KLEIN.
I'M SORRY I BAILED ON YOU THAT
DAY.
I THINK ABOUT IT ALL THE TIME.
&gt;&gt; Klein: D-DAMN IT, KIRITO!
DON'T YOU APOLOGIZE!
DON'T YOU DARE APOLOGIZE NOW!
I WON'T ACCEPT IT!
I'LL NEVER ACCEPT IT UNTIL WE'RE
ON THE OTHER SIDE AND YOU'RE
BUYING ME DINNER, GOD DAMN IT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GOT IT.
SEE YOU ON THE OTHER SIDE.
IF IT'S OKAY, I HAVE A FINAL
REQUEST TO MAKE.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: WHAT IS IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M NOT PLANNING ON
GOING DOWN EASY.
SO IF I DIE TODAY...
I WANT YOUR WORD THAT YOU'LL FIX
IT SO ASUNA DOESN'T KILL
HERSELF.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: AS YOU WISH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO, KIRITO!
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
IT'S NOT FAIR!
[ MACHINE BEEPING ]
KIRITO!!
>> Kirito: THIS ISN'T SOME
IN-GAME DUEL.
IT'S A FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
'CAUSE I'M GONNA KILL HIM!
RRRRRRRAH!
HE CAN BLOCK WHATEVER I THROW
AT HIM 'CAUSE HE DESIGNED THE
DUAL-WIELDING SKILL, AND HE
KNOWS ALL ITS COMBOS.
I HAVE TO BEAT HIM WITH MY OWN
POWER -- WITHOUT USING THE
SWORD SKILLS.
FASTER!
I GOT TO GO FASTER!
RRRRAH!
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: [ CHUCKLES ]
>> Kirito: I'M SORRY, ASUNA.
PLEASE...KEEP LIVING.
RRAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: GAME OVER...
KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
ASUNA.
[ Voice breaking ] ASUNA.
YOU CAN'T...
YOU CAN'T BE...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M SORRY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: GOODBYE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
[ SOBBING ]
>> Akihiko: NOW, THAT WAS A
SURPRISE.
I'M SURE I NEVER PROGRAMMED A
WAY FOR PLAYERS TO NEUTRALIZE
THEIR OWN PARALYSIS.
I GUESS SOMETIMES, THESE THINGS
JUST HAPPEN.
[ SWORD SCRAPES ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ CRUNCH ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
IT'S...OVER NOW.
>> Asuna: I BELIEVE IN YOU...
KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOT YET.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NOT YET!
[ STRAINED GRUNTING ]
GAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ GASPS ]
WE DID IT...DIDN'T WE?
>>ON NOVEMBER 7th AT 2:55 P.M.,
THE GAME HAS BEEN CLEARED.
REPEAT -- THE GAME HAS BEEN
CLEARED.
[ WIND WHISTLING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
WHERE AM I?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
[ WIND GUSTS ]
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I ENDED UP DYING, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES ] DUMMY.
[ RUNNING FOOTSTEPS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHERE ARE WE?
DO YOU KNOW?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: A STUNNING VIEW,
ISN'T IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AKIHIKO KAYABA.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: AT ARGUS
HEADQUARTERS, THE S.A.O.
MAINFRAME IS IN A ROOM FIVE
FLOORS BELOW STREET LEVEL.
AND RIGHT NOW, IT'S DELETING ALL
THE DATA FROM ITS DRIVES.
IN ABOUT 10 MINUTES, EVERYTHING
IN THIS WORLD WILL DISAPPEAR
FOREVER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AND ALL THE PLAYERS?
WHAT HAPPENS TO THEM?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: YOU DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT THEM.
THE 6,147 PLAYERS WHO SURVIVED
THE GAME UP TO NOW WERE LOGGED
OUT A FEW SECONDS AGO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AND WHAT ABOUT THE
4,000 PEOPLE WHO DIED?
WHAT ABOUT THEM?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: THEY'LL NEVER
RETURN.
IN ANY WORLD, REAL OR VIRTUAL,
ONCE YOU'RE DEAD, YOU'RE GONE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY?
WHAT'S THE POINT?
WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: THAT'S A GOOD
QUESTION.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG, I'VE
FORGOTTEN THE REASON.
ISN'T THAT STRANGE?
EVEN BEFORE I DEVELOPED THE
SYSTEM FOR THE FULL-DIVE
ENVIRONMENT, I DREAMED OF
THIS -- A CASTLE IN A WORLD THAT
WASN'T GOVERNED BY EARTHLY LAWS
AND RESTRICTIONS.
I POURED MY LIFE INTO MAKING
THAT WORLD A REALITY.
I CREATED THIS WORLD.
AND I GOT TO SEE SOMETHING THAT
SURPASSED ANYTHING I COULD HAVE
IMAGINED FOR IT.
MY STEEL CASTLE FLOATING IN THE
SKY.
I DON'T REMEMBER HOW OLD I WAS
WHEN I BECAME OBSESSED WITH IT.
I WANTED TO LEAVE THE EARTH,
TO FLY TO THAT CASTLE.
I WANTED THAT MORE THAN ANYTHING
ELSE...FOR AS LONG AS I CAN
REMEMBER.
YOU KNOW WHAT, KIRITO?
I WANT TO BELIEVE IT'S STILL OUT
THERE.
THAT SOMEWHERE, IN SOME OTHER
WORLD, MY CASTLE IS STILL
STANDING, TALLER THAN EVER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
MAYBE IT STILL IS.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: BEFORE I FORGET --
CONGRATULATIONS ON CLEARING THE
GAME, KIRITO, ASUNA.
WELL, THEN, I SHOULD PROBABLY
GET GOING NOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GUESS THIS IS
GOODBYE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MNH-MNH.
THIS ISN'T GOODBYE AT ALL.
WE'RE GONNA BE TOGETHER WHEN WE
FINALLY DISAPPEAR.
SO WE'RE GONNA BE TOGETHER
FOREVER.
HEY, YOU NEVER TOLD ME YOUR REAL
NAME.
WOULD YOU PLEASE TELL ME BEFORE
WE GO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: KAZUTO.
KAZUTO KIRIGAYA.
AND LAST MONTH, I TURNED 16.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: "KAZUTO KIRIGAYA."
[ CHUCKLES ]
SO, YOU'RE YOUNGER THAN ME, HUH?
MY NAME IS ASUNA YUKI.
I'M 17 NOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: "ASUNA YUKI."
"ASUNA YUKI."
[ SNIFFLING ]
SORRY.
[ Voice breaking ] SORRY.
I SWORE, I PROMISED I'D SAVE
YOU -- GET YOU BACK TO THE REAL
WORLD.
BUT I...
I COULDN'T.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M HAPPY I GOT TO MEET YOU,
KAZUTO, AND TO BE WITH YOU...
[ Voice breaking ] AND TO LIVE
WITH YOU.
THIS IS THE HAPPIEST I'VE EVER
BEEN IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
AND I LOVE YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SOBBING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I LOVE YOU...
SO VERY MUCH.
[ MONITOR BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
[ GROANING ]
[ STEADY TONE ]
[ SOBBING ]
A...su...na.
[ Strained ] ASUNA.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]