[ BEEPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, YUI, SEE IF THIS
WILL WORK.
[ RUMBLING ]
&gt;&gt; I'M TRANSFERRING THE CODE.
WE'RE GONNA TELEPORT!
DADDY, GIVE ME YOUR HAND!
DADDY.
DADDY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
YUI. WHERE ARE WE?
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S NO MAPPING DATA
AVAILABLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN DO YOU KNOW
WHERE ASUNA IS?
&gt;&gt; YES.
SHE'S CLOSE -- VERY CLOSE, IN
FACT.
[ GASPS ] THIS WAY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IS THIS IT?
IS THIS THE TOP OF
THE WORLD TREE?
THERE'S SUPPOSED TO BE A
FLOATING CITY UP HERE.
THERE WAS NEVER ANY GRAND QUEST.
THE WHOLE DAMN THING WAS A LIE.
HE'S GONNA PAY FOR THIS.
YEAH, I KNOW.
WE'VE GOT TO GET ASUNA OUT OF
HERE FIRST, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES SOFTLY ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; MOMMY!
MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YUI!
&gt;&gt; MOMMY! MOMMY!
[ BOTH CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA.
HEY. SORRY I TOOK SO LONG.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MNH-MNH.
NO, IT'S OKAY, REALLY.
I ALWAYS KNEW YOU'D SAVE ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL...READY TO GO
HOME?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, YUI, CAN YOU LOG
ASUNA OUT FROM HERE?
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH.
HER STATUS IS LOCKED BY
COMPLICATED CODES THAT I DON'T
HAVE ACCESS TO.
WE'LL NEED TO FIND A SYSTEM
CONSOLE TO BYPASS THEM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I FOUND A CONSOLE IN
THE LABORATORY.
I CAN --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
WHAT'S THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANING ]
[ ALL GRUNT ]
YUI, WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
&gt;&gt; DADDY! MOMMY! BE CAREFUL!
SOMETHING -- SOMETHING BAD'S
COMING!
&gt;&gt; Both: YUI!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
ASUNA.
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT A SURPRISE.
THE LAST THING I EXPECTED TO
FIND WAS A COCKROACH IN MY
LITTLE BIRD'S CAGE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU GOT TO BE
KIDDING!
IT'S SUGOU!
&gt;&gt; MNH-MNH.
I'D PREFER IT IF YOU DIDN'T CALL
ME THAT NAME IN THIS WORLD.
YOU SHOULD ADDRESS ME AS
HIS HIGHNESS, THE FAIRY KING,
OBERON!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; HOW DO YOU LIKE IT?
WANT TO KNOW WHY YOU CAN'T MOVE?
IT'S A LITTLE SOMETHING CALLED
"GRAVITY MAGIC," COMING OUT IN
THE NEXT UPDATE.
YOU THINK THE PLAYERS WILL GO
FOR IT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LEAVE HIM ALONE, YOU
COWARD!
&gt;&gt; TELL ME SOMETHING, KIRIGAYA,
OR SHOULD I CALL YOU "KIRITO"
INSTEAD?
HOW DID YOU MANAGE TO GET ALL
THE WAY UP HERE?
I SAW A STRANGE PROGRAM RUNNING.
IS THAT HOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I FLEW UP HERE WITH
MY WINGS.
&gt;&gt; HA! SUIT YOURSELF.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO TELL ME,
THAT'S FINE.
I'LL JUST GO ASK YOUR MIND
INSTEAD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT?
&gt;&gt; OH, PLEASE.
YOU DON'T REALLY THINK I WENT TO
ALL THAT TROUBLE SETTING THIS
WHOLE THING UP JUST FOR FUN, DID
YOU?
I HAVE 300 FORMER PLAYERS OF
S.A.O. UNDER MY THUMB, AND NOW,
THANKS TO THEIR DEDICATED
COOPERATION, THE TECHNOLOGY I
DEVELOPED FOR TOTAL CONTROL OF
EMOTIONS AND THOUGHT IS 80%
COMPLETE.
I'M ABOUT TO ACHIEVE WHAT NO ONE
ELSE HAS -- THE TOTAL CONTROL OF
THE HUMAN SOUL, THE POWER OF A
GOD!
IT'S SO CLOSE, I CAN ALMOST
TASTE IT!
SERIOUSLY, THANK GOD FOR VIRTUAL
REALITY, HUH?
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SUGOU!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GET
AWAY WITH THIS, YOU HEAR?!
YOU MONSTER!
&gt;&gt; AH, WHO DO YOU THINK'S GOING
TO STOP ME?
OH, MAYBE A GOD.
BUT, SADLY, THERE'S NONE IN THIS
WORLD, EXCEPT FOR YOURS TRULY!
I KNOW -- BEFORE I START
TINKERING WITH YOUR LITTLE
SOULS, WHY DON'T WE HAVE
OURSELVES A LITTLE FUN?!
[ SNAPS FINGERS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU BASTARD!
LEAVE HER ALONE!
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
YES!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HA HA! GREAT!
THAT'S WHAT I WAS HOPING FOR!
YOU CAN'T GET NPC GIRLS TO MAKE
FACES LIKE THAT.
[ SNIFFS ]
AHH. YOU SMELL LOVELY.
FIGURING OUT HOW TO REPLICATE
THE WAY YOU SMELL IN REAL LIFE
WAS A CHALLENGE.
AND DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED ON
HOW [SNIFFS] HARD IT WAS TO GET
AN ANALYZER INTO YOUR HOSPITAL
ROOM UNDETECTED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GET AWAY FROM HER,
SUGOU!
[ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; GIVE ME A BREAK.
WHY DON'T YOU STAY DOWN AND
GROVEL LIKE A GOOD LITTLE DOGGY?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OHH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANING ]
&gt;&gt; SYSTEM COMMAND, CHANGE THE
PAIN ABSORBER FROM LEVEL 10 TO
LEVEL 8.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAAH!
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
HURTS, DOESN'T IT?
I'LL INCREASE THE PAIN GRADUALLY
TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING TO LOOK
FORWARD TO.
BY THE WAY, ONCE IT DROPS BELOW
LEVEL 3, IT'LL START AFFECTING
YOUR BODY IN THE REAL WORLD.
AS FOR YOU...
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: STOP IT, SUGOU!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IT'S OKAY, KIRITO.
WHATEVER HE DOES, HE'S NOT
REALLY HURTING ME.
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
I WAS HOPING YOU'D SAY THAT, BUT
I WONDER HOW LONG YOUR PRIDE'S
GOING TO LAST -- 30 MINUTES, AN
HOUR?
WHY DON'T WE SEE HOW LONG YOU
CAN HANG ON TO IT?!
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
NOW THAT THAT'S OUT OF THE WAY,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO KNOW WHAT I'M
THINKING?
ONCE WE'VE HAD OUR FUN HERE, I'M
GOING TO PAY YOU A VISIT AT THE
HOSPITAL.
I'LL SET UP A BIG MONITOR AND
PLAY BACK A RECORDING OF THIS,
AND WE CAN ENJOY OURSELVES ALL
OVER AGAIN [SLURPS] BUT THIS
TIME, WITH YOUR REAL BODY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
AH. YUMMY. HOW SWEET.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SUGOU, YOU BASTARD!
YOU BASTARD!
&gt;&gt; MMM!
[ LAUGHS MANIACALLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL KILL YOU!
YOU HEAR?!
I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
[ GRUNTING ]
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
AM I BEING PUNISHED FOR
THINKING I WAS SOME KIND OF
HERO, FOR THINKING I WAS THE
ONLY ONE WHO COULD SAVE ASUNA,
FOR THINKING I WAS STRONG
ENOUGH, EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: ARE YOU GIVING UP?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO.
I'M FACING REALITY.
>> Akihiko: THEN YOU AREGIVING
UP -- TO THE POWER OF A SYSTEM
YOU ONCE DEFIED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT CHOICE DO I
HAVE?
I'M JUST A PLAYER, AND HE'S THE
G.M.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: THEN OUR BATTLE WAS,
WHAT, A JOKE?
DO YOU REMEMBER HOW YOU SHOWED
ME THE POWER OF THE HUMAN WILL
WAS SUPERIOR TO THE SYSTEM, HOW
YOU SHOWED ME THE POSSIBILITIES
OF THE FUTURE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE...
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: GET UP, KIRITO.
GET UP!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; AHH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANING ]
YOUR ATTACKS ARE WEAK.
THE BLADES IN S.A.O. HIT WAY
HARDER!
AND THEY HURT WAY MORE!
[ GROANS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
&gt;&gt; UNBELIEVABLE.
I'VE GOT A FEW BUGS LEFT TO DEAL
WITH.
YAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SYSTEM LOG-IN.
I.D. HEATHCLIFF.
&gt;&gt; WH-WHAT?
WHOSE I.D. ARE YOU USING?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SYSTEM COMMAND,
ENABLE ADMINISTRATOR PRIVILEGES.
SET I.D. OBERON TO LEVEL 1.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
AN I.D. THAT OUTRANKS MINE?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
THIS IS MY WORLD!
I'M THE CREATOR!
I'M ITS RULER, ITS KING, ITS
GOD!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU STOLE EVERYTHING IN THIS
WORLD -- EVERYTHING -- INCLUDING
ITS PEOPLE.
YOU'RE NOTHING BUT A KING OF
THIEVES, SITTING ALONE ON YOUR
STOLEN THRONE!
&gt;&gt; YOU LITTLE PUNK.
YOU DARE -- YOU DARE TALK TO ME
LIKE THAT?!
SYSTEM COMMAND, GENERATE OBJECT!
I.D. EXCALIBUR!
DO AS I SAY, YOU PIECE OF CRAP!
SYSTEM, YOUR GOD IS ORDERING YOU
TO COMPLY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THINK YOU CAN WAIT A
LITTLE BIT LONGER?
THIS WILL ONLY TAKE A SEC.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SYSTEM COMMAND,
GENERATE OBJECT!
I.D. EXCALIBUR!
A SIMPLE COMMAND SUMMONS A
LEGENDARY WEAPON.
WHO KNEW?
&gt;&gt; HUH! UH!
HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S TIME TO SETTLE
THE SCORE --
THE KING OF THIEVES VERSUS
THE GILDED HERO!
SYSTEM COMMAND, SET PAIN
ABSORBER TO ZERO!
&gt;&gt; NO, NOT THAT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DID YOU JUST FLINCH?
'CAUSE THE OTHER GUY NEVER
FLINCHED, NO MATTER HOW BAD
THINGS GOT.
YOU KNOW HIM -- AKIHIKO KAYABA!
&gt;&gt; OH, MY GOD! KAYABA?!
OH, I GET IT.
THAT WAS HISI.D.
WHY?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE DEAD!
WHY ARE YOU STILL GETTING IN MY
WAY?!
YOU ARE ALWAYS DOING THIS,
ACTING ALL HIGH AND MIGHTY, LIKE
SOME BIG SHOT, TAKING EVERYTHING
THAT WAS RIGHTFULLY MINE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SUGOU, IN A WAY, I
GET WHERE YOU'RE COMING FROM.
I LOST TO HIM, TOO, AND THEN I
HAD TO GO WORK FOR HIM.
BUT WHATEVER HAPPENED, I NEVER
WANTED TO BE HIM, UNLIKE YOU.
&gt;&gt; DAMN YOU!
GOD DAMN YOU!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAH!
AAH! AAH!
[ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HURTS, DOESN'T IT?
BUT IT'S NOTHING LIKE THE PAIN
YOU MADE ASUNA FEEL -- NOT EVEN
CLOSE!
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
MY HAND!
MY HAND! MY HAND!
[ WHIMPERING ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ GROANING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERING CONTINUES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I HAD FAITH IN YOU.
I HAVE FAITH IN YOU.
ALWAYS HAVE, ALWAYS WILL.
AND I KNOW YOU'LL ALWAYS SAVE ME
BECAUSE YOU ARE MY HERO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I-I DON'T HAVE ANY
POWER.
I'M NOT A HERO.
[ CRYING CONTINUES ]
I-I'LL DO MY BEST TO BE ONE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON.
LET'S GO HOME.
IT'S GOT TO BE NIGHTTIME ALREADY
BACK THERE, BUT I'LL SEE YOU AT
THE HOSPITAL AS SOON AS I CAN.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'LL BE WAITING FOR
YOU.
I WANT YOU TO BE THE FIRST
PERSON I SEE WHEN I WAKE UP.
[ GASPS ]
IT'S FINALLY OVER, ISN'T IT?
WE'RE GOING HOME -- BACK TO THE
REAL WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT A LOT'S CHANGED, SO TRY NOT
TO FREAK OUT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ CHUCKLES ]
LET'S GO PLACES AND DO FUN
THINGS, JUST THE TWO OF US.
SOUND GOOD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH -- REAL GOOD.
THAT'S IT.
GAME OVER.
OR IS IT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK, HEATHCLIFF?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: GOOD TO SEE YOU
AGAIN, KIRITO.
>> Kirito: SO, YOU AREALIVE.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: YOU COULD SAY I'M
ALIVE, IN A WAY.
ULTIMATELY, I'M THE AFTERIMAGE
OF THE MIND THAT WAS
AKIHIKO KAYABA -- AN ECHO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AND, AS USUAL, I HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT.
I GUESS I SHOULD THANK YOU,
THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: THAT'S NOT
NECESSARY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: WE'RE NOT EXACTLY
FRIENDS, SO WE SHOULDN'T EXPECT
FAVORS FROM EACH OTHER.
THERE'S ALWAYS A PRICE --
ALWAYS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
WHAT'S THIS?
&gt;&gt; Akihiko: THE BEGINNINGS OF A
NEW WORLD.
I CALL IT "THE SEED."
ONCE IT SPROUTS, YOU'LL KNOW
WHAT IT IS.
WHAT YOU DO WITH IT IS UP TO
YOU.
YOU CAN EVEN DELETE IT IF YOU
WANT.
HOWEVER, IF YOU STILL HAVE A
TINY BIT OF FONDNESS LEFT FOR
THE VIRTUAL WORLD, YOU'LL TAKE
CARE OF IT.
I SHOULD GET GOING NOW.
I DO HOPE WE MEET AGAIN, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI! ARE YOU OKAY?!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
&gt;&gt; DADDY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANK GOD.
YOU'RE SAFE.
&gt;&gt; UH-HUH.
I HID MYSELF INSIDE THE LOCAL
MEMORY OF YOUR NerveGear RIG.
WHERE'S MOMMY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T WORRY.
SHE'S SAFE.
SHE'S BACK HOME NOW.
&gt;&gt; MOMMY'S BACK?!
THANK GOODNESS!
[ Crying ] I'M SO HAPPY --
REALLY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I PROMISE WE'LL BE
BACK TO VISIT SOON, ALTHOUGH I
DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH LONGER THIS
WORLD'S GONNA BE AROUND.
&gt;&gt; IT DOESN'T MATTER BECAUSE MY
CORE PROGRAM'S INSIDE YOUR
NerveGear NOW, SO WE'LL ALWAYS
BE TOGETHER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ALL RIGHT.
I'D BETTER HEAD OUT.
I'M GONNA GO SEE MOMMY.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, DADDY.
I-I LOVE YOU!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SMOOCHES ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] AAH!
I-I'M SORRY!
WHEN YOU DIDN'T LOG OUT RIGHT
AWAY, I GOT WORRIED, AND THEN
I --
&gt;&gt; SORRY I TOOK SO LONG TO COME
BACK.
&gt;&gt; IS IT REALLY OVER NOW?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, IT IS.
IT'S ALL OVER.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] THAT'S AWESOME!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
HEY, SUGU, THANK YOU FOR ALL THE
HELP YOU GAVE ME.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT ON MY
OWN.
YOU'RE THE REASON I WAS ABLE TO
FINISH IT.
&gt;&gt; NO.
&gt;&gt; UGH!
&gt;&gt; YOU DON'T HAVE TO THANK ME
FOR A THING.
I'M JUST HAPPY I GOT THE CHANCE
TO HELP MY BIG BROTHER IN HIS
WORLD.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT HAPPENED WITH ASUNA?
DID YOU GET HER BACK?
&gt;&gt; UH-HUH, FINALLY.
SHE'S BACK IN THE REAL WORLD.
SUGU, I, UH --
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH. YOU GET GOING.
SHE'S GOT TO BE WONDERING WHERE
YOU'RE AT BY NOW.
&gt;&gt; OHH. IT'S COLD.
&gt;&gt; LOOK -- SNOW.
BE CAREFUL OUT THERE AND SAY HI
TO ASUNA FOR ME.
&gt;&gt; YOU GOT IT.
I CAN'T WAIT FOR YOU GUYS TO
MEET FOR REAL!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]