[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan, Bulma and Krillin were
on their way to Planet Namek,
when they were taken hostage by
a militant group of refugees.
These heavily armed soldiers
believed our three heroes
to be allies
of Frieza,
who had recently
destroyed their home planet.
[BULMA whimpering]
[NARRATOR] After a few
tense moments,
the case of mistaken
identity was cleared,
and the leader of the group
told the horrifying tale
of his planet's
destruction.
Frieza's henchmen had
descended upon his world
and destroyed
everything in their path.
They were cruel and merciless,
with a power even more terrible
than that of
the Saiyans!
[NARRATOR] But as awful as
this story was,
there was little time
for our heroes to ponder
the identity of these
mysterious marauders.
For as soon as they resumed
their journey to Namek,
they had problems of
their own to worry about!
[NARRATOR] Bulma's travel
plans landed the ship
right in the middle of a
fierce interstellar storm
caused by a recently
exploded nebula!
Then, as the ship was thrown
clear of the turbulence...
[BULMA] Yes! It's Namek!
We finally made it!
Are you
sure that's...
[GOHAN]
Planet Namek?
[BULMA] Trust me,
it's the right planet.
Now, let's go and find
those Dragon Balls!
We're about to
start our descent.
Strap yourselves
in nice and tight.
It's gonna be
a rough landing.
[GOHAN] Right.
Brace yourselves!
It looks like we've got
a rough ride ahead of us!
[GOHAN and KRILLIN yelling]
[ALL whimpering]
[BULMA] We made it!
And in one piece!
[GOHAN] Great! I can't
wait to see how it looks!
But, there's a lot
of fog right now.
[KRILLIN] Yeah.
Are you sure this
is Planet Namek?
It better be.
Yeah, but...
Oh, are you trying to
say that I don't know how
to navigate a
spaceship? Is that it?!
No, Bulma. I just
want to be sure!
Come on!
Spit it out!
The Dragon Radar
could tell us
what planet
we're on, you know.
He's right!
Fine... I can't believe
you don't trust me.
[BULMA gasps]
[ALL screaming]
Uh, hello.
[laughing]
Looks like
she's awake now.
Who are you?
[RAITI] I'm Raiti.
You're looking at the worst
doctor on this planet.
Very funny... Pay no
attention to Zaacro.
He's been a thorn in my side
for three hundred years.
What? Three
hundred years?!
[ZAACRO] Nice to
meet you, Miss.
Heh, heh, heh, heh...
That's the greeting
on this planet.
Oh... Likewise.
You know... You should
feel very lucky
that we happened to
find you when we did...
I was able to treat your
injuries in time to save you,
but it was close.
All three of you
were near death.
Thanks for saving us.
Hey, come on guys. Time to wake
up. We've got to get going.
Uh, hey!
[KRILLIN]
Nice to meet you.
[BULMA] This is
Planet Namek, right?
[RAITI]
Sure is.
You guys look very
familiar to me...
Have you ever been
to Earth before?
No, Krillin... They just
happen to look like Piccolo.
You know we'd like to help
you find your Dragon Balls.
[gasping]
How'd you
know that?
[RAITI chuckling]
[ALL gasping]
We know just
about everything
there is to know
about you guys.
Well, if there's one species
capable of doing that...
It would
definitely be a Namek.
Don't worry,
you can trust us.
We won't take
advantage of you.
Do you know what happened
to our spaceship?
Yes. It's safe. We put
it in our storage garage.
[ZAACRO]
Here it is.
[BULMA] Oh, look
how banged up it is!
I'm glad it's
still in one piece.
[ZAACRO] Me, too.
[GOHAN] Are you always this
nice to complete strangers?
[RAITI] Only with
the ones we like.
Heh. Then I guess
it's a wonderful thing
that we're on your good side,
eh? Thanks for your help.
[RAITI and ZAACRO chuckling]
Look, guys!
I got a signal!
[KRILLIN] Oh, that's great!
[GOHAN and KRILLIN laughing]
Check this out!
It looks like we've got
three Dragon Balls
in the
immediate area.
[KRILLIN] Lucky us!
[GOHAN] Let's start
looking now!
If we hurry, we could find
them all by the end of the day.
[KRILLIN] Yeah! Let's do it!
[BULMA] You gotta
love Capsule Corp.!
[GOHAN] Yeah!
[RAITI] I wouldn't take
that if I were you.
[BULMA] What?
The outlying territories are
teeming with hundred foot tall,
five hundred ton monsters,
that wouldn't think twice of
stepping on your little car.
It's highly recommended that
everyone travel by air.
Trust me!
Monsters?
[roaring]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
Uh... Bulma?
Well, I'm in
a good mood.
I'll take you there
myself in the Wukong.
[BULMA] Wukong?
[engine puttering]
[puttering continues]
[whimpering]
Now, be honest...
What do you think?
Isn't my Wukong one
beast of a ship?
[BULMA]
Jackpot!
Excuse me!
The Radar--
It says the Dragon Ball
is right below us!
No problem. Wukong,
start your descent right now!
[ALL screaming]
[hammer clanking]
It's gonna take a miracle to
get this ship fully repaired.
Any luck?
[GOHAN]
Not yet.
[BULMA] Keep searching. It's got
to be around here somewhere!
You can rest
if you want...
You've helped
us out enough already.
No worries.
I really have nothing
better to do now, anyway.
Well, thank you...
Back on earth we're
having a bit of a crisis
without the Dragon Balls
in our possession.
But you already
know that, right?
Yup.
The Radar is telling
me the Dragon Ball
should be ten yards
out that way.
You find it?
[KRILLIN] Uh-uh, uh-uhh.
We're having trouble holding
our breath long enough.
[GOHAN] It's not easy.
The river is really deep.
Well, the Dragon
Radar has never given
a false reading yet.
Hey... Where's Raiti?
[RAITI] Got it!
[KRILLIN] Ha-haa!
[GOHAN] Yeah!
Here it is!
Ha, ha, ha! All right!
What happened?!
[SUBORDINATE] Uh, well,
sir, we don't know!
All his readings
are in the green.
[SUBORDINATE] He's fully
conscious now!
[VEGETA] Kakarot!
[APE GOHAN roaring]
[VEGETA thinking]
I don't get it.
I'm much stronger
than him in battle!
Yet, I'm the one taking
on all the damage!
It's as if his power
has increased ten-fold!
[GOKU] Haah!
[CHICHI screams]
[PATIENT yells]
Uh?
What are you doing?!
You almost hit me!
Ouch, that hurt.
Why can't you
just lay there
and sleep like a
normal patient?!
You're bothering
everyone!
Because I'm not a
normal patient!
I'm a fighter! I need
to get out of this place!
Oh, Goku. Stop talking
like such a tough guy!
You're injured, and the only
way you're gonna get better
is if you just lay
here and stay quiet.
Is that gonna
be for me?
Goku, do you
really think
you'll be able
to fit into this?
I could at
least try.
[RAITI] These are ruins
from a city that existed
five thousand
years ago.
[KRILLIN]
That's amazing!
Okay, according
to the Radar,
the second Dragon Ball should
be fifty meters from us.
Bulma, look.
There.
You see it?
[KRILLIN] There're some
stairs leading below.
[BULMA] Yeah, the signal's
getting stronger.
Let's check
it out, then.
[BULMA] Come on,
let's follow him.
[KRILLIN]
Right behind you.
[GOHAN] Wow. These
drawings must be from
the ancient
Namek people.
[KRILLIN]
Are you sure?
Because these drawings don't
look like normal Nameks,
unless they've changed over
the years. Could that be?
Well, no two
Nameks look alike.
[KRILLIN] We're inside
of a tomb, aren't we?
[GOHAN] There may be
a treasure down here!
We're getting really
close now, guys.
[BULMA]
Here it is.
Ah! Be careful!
[stammering in fear]
[BULMA screaming]
Okay! Two down and one
Dragon Ball to go!
He's really
nice, isn't he?
Yeah, you don't see
that much on Earth...
Someone willing to help
a complete stranger.
But that's exactly what
I find suspicious.
We should be careful,
because for all we know,
he's just using us so that once
we get all seven Dragon Balls,
he can steal them!
No way.
It's below
us now.
Could you set the ship
down softly, please?
Setting down!
[BULMA squealing]
[BULMA]
That's strange.
[RAITI]
What's the matter?
Somehow the Dragon
Ball is moving.
[BULMA] Woah!
Are you
okay, Bulma?
[BULMA] I'm okay,
but my Radar is telling--
Huh?
[BULMA screams]
Can I have
that, please?
[BULMA whimpering]
[BULMA] Wait!
Come back!
[KRILLIN] Bulma!
[BULMA] Give me back
that Dragon Ball!
It can't understand
a word you're saying!
[RAITI] Wait, stop!
[BULMA]
What are you doing?!
We mustn't go any
further into the forest!
We have to hurry!
He's getting away!
Why did you stop me?
We lost him!
It's much too dangerous
to go on foot from here.
Huh?
Oh, that's
just great!
Why did you let
him get away?!
You're planning on stealing
the Dragon Balls
from us, aren't you?!
Tell me the truth!
I-I wouldn't think
of such a thing.
I'm keeping my
eye on you.
Something funny's
going on here,
and I'm gonna
figure it out.
[distant roaring]
That didn't sound normal...
Something's happened to it.
[RAITI] Let's find out.
[RAITI] The sound we heard most
likely came from here.
[KRILLIN] Whoa!
Is that a skeleton?
[RAITI] It must be the
monster we just saw.
This swamp can melt any
living creature in seconds.
Why, I've heard tales
that even the fumes
can kill a Namek
from a single breath!
Is that right? Now I see why
you stopped me before.
I'm sorry I yelled at
you. I had no idea.
[RAITI] I just didn't want
you to get hurt.
You're too nice!
[KRILLIN] Hey guys,
we've got a problem here.
Since the monster is
obviously dead in the swamp...
Then that means
the Dragon Ball
must be somewhere
on the bottom!
And if that swamp
melts us instantly,
then how are we
gonna get it back?
It's impossible.
Are you sure?
We do have a
protective body suit
we use for
underwater operations.
But the material
it's made of
is not strong enough
to handle the swamp.
After about 20 seconds,
it begins to rapidly melt.
I'm gonna do it.
[ALL] What?
We have to retrieve
the Dragon Ball
at all costs,
isn't that right?
Well, yeah, I guess
so, but I--
So, all I have to do is surface
within 20 seconds to be safe.
Come on, it's at
least worth a try!
Oh, I know!
We'll tie a special rope
to him and pull him out
before twenty
seconds is up.
Then we can be sure
you get out safely.
That's a
good idea.
Okay, then
let's get to it.
It says the Dragon Ball
is directly below us...
Just be quick.
We'll start pulling you up
at thirteen seconds, okay?
Right.
[ALL] Three...
Four... Five...
Oh no!
I underestimated how potent
the water was going to be!
[BULMA] Gohan!
[KRILLIN] Gohan!
[thinking] That was
easier than I thought.
All right, pull
me up, Raiti...
Oh no, the rope!
I'm gonna
have to hurry!
[thinking] I'm running
out of time!
It's gonna eat right
through the suit!
[thinking] I can't
hold on any longer!
Flashing Attack!
Haah!
Gohan...
[GOHAN grunting]
[BOTH] Gohan!
Got it!
Yeah!
Awesome!
Easy! You're
squeezing too hard.
[NARRATOR]
Though they have found three
of the seven Dragon Balls,
each one has been more
difficult to retrieve.
And far away,
Vegeta slowly awakens
from his
recuperating slumber.
Will revenge
be on his mind?
Find out on the next
Dragon Ball Z!