[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z!
Kami finally agreed
to unite with Piccolo.
No Kami, don't!
[yells]
[NARRATOR] It was a difficult
decision to say the least,
but in his wisdom, and in spite
of the great personal cost,
Kami chose to do what he felt
was best for the earth!
His fusion with Piccolo
would be a noble sacrifice,
after which Kami
would no longer exist
and Piccolo would
be changed forever.
[NARRATOR] Their union complete,
Piccolo stood reborn.
Now that Kami's
vast knowledge and power
had been added to his own,
Piccolo was no longer
his former self.
He had become a Super Namek!
I'll miss you. Good-bye, Kami.
Oh... Please be careful.
No longer am I Kami or Piccolo.
I am the Namek who has
long since forgotten his name.
[NARRATOR] While Mr. Popo
bade a final reluctant farewell
to his old friend,
the new and improved Piccolo
made his way down to the earth,
where beneath a
seemingly tranquil surface
a sinister evil laid in wait.
[NARRATOR] His newfound Super
Namek powers still untested,
Piccolo has come
face to face with the most
diabolical creature
ever to walk the earth!
[NARRATOR]
The fate of the planet
rests on Piccolo's
mighty shoulders!
But is the noble
Namek warrior prepared for
what this hideous monster
has in store?
The new face
of evil has arrived!
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
At last we meet...
face to face...
[CREATURE growls lowly]
[PICCOLO] Hmmm?!
Hey, you gotta help me,
please! Help me!
What the...?!
What am I sensing
from that thing?!
His... power...
I've sensed it
somewhere before!
Please, I beg of you!
You have to help me! Please!
Please! I'm in more than
a little pain here!
This doesn't look good.
I'm afraid this new monster,
it may be too powerful.
[POPO] Even with
their strengths combined,
Kami and Piccolo may not
be able to win this fight!
[POPO] Oh, Kami...
If there was only
something I could do...
[MAN A] C'mon!
What're you waiting for?!
Help me!
Listen! I'm the
richest man in town
and I'll give you
whatever you want!
Here, take this! And there's
more where that came from!
[grunts]
Hey! Are you listening?!
You would be wise
to let him go.
You've done enough already.
It's time you picked on
someone your own size!
[groans, grunts]
Oh, thank you!
Here, take my money, all of it!
[MAN A] Oh, you saved my life!
I'll give you everything I have!
Oh, thank you!
[yelps]
Hm?!
[groans]
[yells]
[MAN A gasps, groans]
[CREATURE] Now that
we've gotten that vermin
out of the way...
You're next, Piccolo.
[gasps]
[PICCOLO] Wh-What did you say?
[growls]
[yells]
This... can't be...!
What's going on?!
[CREATURE grunts]
Uuuh? Huh?
Hey, what's eatin' ya, Gohan?
I know it's weird,
but I can sense two Piccolos!
Huh? Two Piccolos?
Huh?
--[YAMCHA grunts]
--[ROSHI] Hm...
Whoa... He's right...!
[CREATURE chuckles]
What's the matter?
You seem afraid, Piccolo.
No! Far from it, in fact!
Now tell me
how you know that name!
Well... one might say
that we're brothers.
What?!
[laughs]
Ah... Gohan. Are you
sensing what I'm sensing?
It's... Frieza...!
And his father!
What?! That's ridiculous!
What's going on?
My father and Piccolo...
They're in Gingertown...!
And if I didn't know better,
I'd say Frieza was with them!
Frieza... He's here
with his father...?
But that's madness!
No... I sense it too!
But... that's impossible!
I thought Trunks destroyed
Frieza and his father!
Yeah, well so did I!
Me too! But it feels like
they're both alive
and well in Gingertown!
Uh. Uuh!
--[YAMCHA] Ah!
--[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN] Holy cow...
Do you guys feel that?
It's... Goku!
Yeah! He's there too!
[grunts]
But my dad's
still here sleeping!
[ALL gasp]
I'm nearing section 1051.
That's close to where we found
that weird creature's shell...
and Gingertown!
Now, if you think you've
finished showing off...
I want answers. Who are you?
[grunts]
[CREATURE] Silly Piccolo...
My secrets will not
be unlocked so easily.
[grunts]
No matter.
I'll still destroy you...
[PICCOLO] whoever you are.
[CREATURE] You're even more
amusing than I imagined.
Heh.
Well, we'll see if
you still feel that way
after I've beaten you.
[CREATURE chuckles]
Such a fighter's spirit!
I will enjoy
absorbing you, Piccolo.
[PICCOLO]
You keep using that name.
It seems you've mistaken
me for someone else.
[grunts] So...
[PICCOLO] Allow me
to introduce myself!
[PICCOLO grunts, groans]
[grunts, growls]
[PICCOLO] The Piccolo
that you know is gone.
[grunts]
I am "The Namek!"
[PICCOLO]
And as for you... well...
You're history!
Hm?!
[chuckles]
[PICCOLO grunts]
I'm impressed, Namek!
[CREATURE]
Your power is astounding!
I'm sure you will prove
to be a most satisfying meal!
Don't count on it!
Oh good.
I'm glad I found you.
We've been sensing
all sorts of weirdness
coming from Gingertown,
and we thought you
might need some help.
Thanks. I was sort of
thinking the same thing.
I'm not really sure
what to make of any of this.
Wait a sec...
Something's happening!
Yeah. I noticed it
a minute ago.
[TRUNKS]
It's a huge power level...
but I can't tell whose it is!
[laughing]
I think it's Piccolo!
[KRILLIN]
Ha-ha! He did it! Yeah!
What did he do?
Must've been something
pretty radical
if he's changed this much.
That's right, Trunks!
He's united with Kami!
[TRUNKS] United? Wait...
You told me about this before!
You said that Piccolo and Kami
were originally one being,
and that if they ever
reunited they'd be
even stronger
than a Super Saiyan!
Yep, that's right.
Piccolo's become a Super Namek!
Super Namek...
His power level must be amazing!
[PICCOLO grunting]
You know, you've made
one critical mistake.
You never should have
emptied this city
of its entire population!
Why is that?
[PICCOLO]
Because as long as there are
no innocent bystanders
to get in the way,
I'm free to fight you
with the best of my ability!
[CREATURE]
So what's stopping you?
[PICCOLO] You know,
that's a really good question!
[CREATURE] Hmmm?
[grunting]
[grunts]
[yelling]
[PICCOLO grunts, yells]
[CREATURE yells]
[gasps]
Well, it looks like
the battle's started!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, no kidding!
I sure hope Piccolo wasn't
on the wrong end of that blast!
[tires screech]
[birds chirpping]
Hmmm.
[ANDROID 18] What was that?
[ANDROID 17] It felt like
some sort of an explosion.
And a big one, too.
I wonder what it was.
It was much too far away
to tell where it came from.
[car door opens]
[ANDROID 16]
It came from Gingertown.
[ANDROID 17 and 18] Hm?
[ANDROID 16] Two enormous
powers are fighting there.
Hm...
[ANDROID 17] You mean your
sensors can detect power levels?
Why didn't you
tell us that before?
Because you did not ask!
All right. Fair enough.
Now I don't suppose
you can tell me
who it is that's
fighting, can you?
[ANDROID 16] No, I cannot.
I do not recognize
either of these powers.
My sensors indicate
that one of the fighters
is just as strong as you, 17.
What's that?
[ANDROID 16]
My sensors indicate that--
Quiet! I heard what you said
quite clearly the first time.
Your "sensors"
must be malfunctioning!
Nobody is as strong as I am.
I'm the most powerful
fighter there is!
[ANDROID 17 scoffs]
Really! "As strong as I am!"
[car door slams shut]
[ANDROID 18] Let's go, 16.
[CREATURE groans]
Hmmm?
[grunts]
[groans]
[CREATURE yells]
[growls lowly]
[CREATURE chuckles]
[CREATURE]
Special Beam Cannon!
[PICCOLO grunts]
He's good...
[CREATURE yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
[CREATURE] Huh? Ah...!
[grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts]
I must admit...
You're a lot stronger
than I gave you credit for.
But don't let that
go to your head.
[laughs]
You have yet to see my
true strength.
I was not able to gather
enough energy in this city
to reach my full power.
Your full power?
Ah huh...
Ugh! Monster!
That's why you absorbed
all those innocent people!
[chuckles] Yes.
It is their living energy
that gives me my power!
[grunting]
Who are you?!
What kind of a twisted mind
would think to send you here
in that time machine?
Huh?
[PICCOLO] Answer me!
[laughs]
I came here of my own accord!
Huh?
[CREATURE] The time capsule
was much too small for me
to fit inside
while in my present state.
I was forced to
regress to my larval form
and enclose myself
within an egg.
Pretty ingenious,
don't you think?
[CREATURE] Yes. You seem
to know much, Piccolo.
But there is still
much for you to learn!
Uh...?
[laughs]
[gasps]
[growls lowly]
Oh man...
What's going on down there?
I... I'm sensing Goku again!
Ah...
[CREATURE] Ka...
Me...
[CREATURE] Ha...
It... can't be!
[grunts]
Fa-Father...?
[stammers]
No! What's going on?!
Haaaa!