[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z...
Goku,
beaten and weary,
gave Krillin all of
his remaining energy
to fuel an attack
on the evil Vegeta.
[VEGETA screaming]
[NARRATOR] But instead
of defeating him,
it only sent the Saiyan
into a furious rage...
[VEGETA yelling]
[NARRATOR] As the Earth
crumbled around him,
Vegeta's power
seemed unstoppable.
His victory
was certain,
until he made an
unsettling discovery
about the
young Gohan.
It can't be!
He... He has a tail!
Which way?
Let's see, turn to
the left a little bit...
[CHICHI] Do you see anything?
Are we almost there?
[KORIN] Keep your shirt
on, I'm looking...
Hey! I think
I see it!
That's the island where Goku
and the others are fighting!
[CHICHI] Can you tell
if they're alright?
My husband? My son?
How are they? Tell me!
Please...
stop... choking...
I'll choke all nine
lives out of you
[CHICHI] unless you answer me!
[KORIN] I... don't... know!
You kids be good or we'll
have to pull this thing over...
[thinking] Goku, I can
only hope that you've
put an end to
this by now.
You're the only
chance this world has
against that
monster...
Gohan's tail...
I forgot about that...
It must have
grown back...
[VEGETA] The Blutz Waves!
I can't allow this brat
to transform! Not today!
Haah...
[YAJIROBE]
Leave him alone!
[VEGETA] What?
[YAJIROBE yelling]
[VEGETA screaming]
[VEGETA] You cut
through my armor!
[VEGETA shouting]
[YAJIROBE laughing]
[laughing continues]
I got him! I got him!
I beat you, dirtbag!
I can see it now...
Earth's greatest threat
brought down by Yajirobe!
Oh, yeah! Took him down!
You should learn not
to mess with the best!
You can't
handle it!
[YAJIROBE chuckling]
What was that, tubby?
[YAJIROBE] Uh...
Wait a minute!
Hey, hold on!
I was...
I was just kidding about
the whole dirtbag thing!
You really thought I was
trying to hurt you, didn't you?
That's funny! I was just
messing around with you!
[YAJIROBE] No, wait! Listen!
I don't think you understand!
That... hurt...
[KRILLIN] Oh, no!
How dare you! No one
attacks me on my blind side
and gets away
with it! No one!
[VEGETA] Don't... you... ever...
do... that... again!
Yajirobe...
[GOKU thinking] Gohan...
Gohan, can you hear me? Gohan!
[GOHAN] Uh... Hello?
[GOKU thinking]
Gohan, listen to me!
Daddy...?
[GOKU thinking] Look at the
power ball in the sky, Gohan...
But, I don't understand...
Dad, where are you?
[GOKU thinking] I'm not far
away, but I need your help.
You can help me by staring
up at that light in the sky.
[GOKU thinking]
That's it, Gohan...
Don't turn away from it...
The boy's tail!
I've got to stop him!
[VEGETA] It's too late!
[VEGETA] No!
Stop changing! Stop it!
He's transforming
into the ape!
[thinking] Yes, Gohan!
You can do it!
Gohan!
He's changing!
That fake moon
made him transform!
The tail! I've got
to cut off his tail
before he goes
completely berserk!
Right now!
[APE GOHAN roaring]
[VEGETA grunting]
[roaring continues]
[APE GOHAN howling]
Gohan...
He's... He's
out of control!
Gohan's just a mindless,
raging beast now!
It's just like when
Goku used to change!
He doesn't
remember anything!
As long as he's like that, he's
just as dangerous as Vegeta!
Gohan, stop it!
Oh man, I've just got to
think of some way
to get through to him!
But how? When Goku
was like this,
he didn't
recognize any of us!
[YAJIROBE] Help!
Somebody please help me!
[KRILLIN] Gohan! Wait!
We're your friends!
[GOKU thinking]
Gohan! Stop!
No! Gohan!
What happened?
[KRILLIN] Hey! Gohan!
Get the other guy!
Hurry! He's getting away!
Hey, don't
get him excited!
I'm... I'm trapped!
Now!
[APE GOHAN roaring]
I'm glad
I'm not him!
Gohan!
Smash that guy now!
Somehow, Goku must
have gotten through
to Gohan
telepathically...
Finish him, Gohan!
It's all up to you, now!
My moon's going to shine
for at least another hour,
and there's no way I can
keep outrunning him!
I've got to cut
off that tail!
Man, he's tough!
He punched Gohan's head in!
This guy's insane!
Can't anybody stop him?
Haaa!
Okay, fur-ball...
Take this!
Wait! I can't
get around him!
[VEGETA screaming]
Hey! What's happening?
[GOHAN snoring,
VEGETA whimpering]
He... He got him!
[snoring continues]
Gohan beat him?
Spoke too soon...
[VEGETA grunting]
[INVESTIGATOR 1] Let's get
these two loaded in the truck.
I want a team to
take them apart
and examine
them thoroughly
before we crate them up and
claim that they don't exist.
[electronic beeping]
[INVESTIGATOR 2] Whoa...
Did you hear that?
Aahh!
[KRILLIN]
What is that thing?
What's it doing?
[VEGETA] Yes! It's here!
Ha! Those fools! They haven't
seen the last of me...
I'm Vegeta! The strongest
Saiyan in the universe...
I'm Invincible!
It-It must be his space
ship! I've gotta stop him.
[VEGETA]
Almost... There...
Krillin! Use my
sword! Hurry up!
[thinking] The sword...
Yeah, this thing cut
through his armor!
It might just
come in handy...
[KRILLIN]
Hey, Saiyan!
[KRILLIN] You think you can
just slither out of here
after what you've
done? Well...
Think again!
No... No! You can't
do this to me!
[KING KAI] Yes! They've
stopped those Saiyans!
I'm so relieved...
Goku and his friends
did a good job!
They stood together
and saved their planet...
He's really
come a long way!
Goku did things I didn't
think he was capable of!
Amazing!
But, I... I sense that
there's an even greater evil
headed their way...
[KING KAI] These Saiyans
are only the beginning...
[KRILLIN] Urryaaughh!
[GOKU] Stop!
[GOKU] Don't do it!
[KRILLIN]
Goku? Is that you?
We've... We have got
to stop this guy
while we
have the chance!
He's... He's pure evil...
No! Listen...
Just let him go, Krillin...
Show him what it means
to be merciful...
Merciful?!
But... Goku, he's--
[GOKU] I know what you
must be thinking, Krillin,
but believe me.
I know what I'm doing...
But this is the guy
that threatened
all of the people
here on Earth!
Surely he'll try to come
back and destroy us again!
I just don't think it's a
good idea to let him escape
now that we have a chance
to stop him for good!
[GOKU] By doing this,
we're showing him
that there is another
way, a better way!
[KRILLIN] Goku, I don't think
this is the kind of guy
that can learn a
lesson like that!
He'll just think we're weak!
It won't change him at all.
[GOKU] Don't be so sure
about that, Krillin.
It wouldn't be the first time
something like that happened.
Think about it...
When Piccolo
first came to us,
he was just as evil
as his father had been.
He nearly destroyed not only
me, but the entire planet!
And now?
And now, he's one of us!
[GOKU] Right! And if someone
as evil as Piccolo can change,
I think anyone can!
[GOKU] Vegeta deserves
to have that same chance!
By showing him that the
people of this planet
have compassion and
can show mercy,
maybe he can learn to
show some of his own.
Piccolo learned, and now he's
not only a powerful ally,
he's also a
good friend.
He even took care of
Gohan while I was gone,
and traded his own life
to protect him. Who knows?
Vegeta might do the same thing
for one of us someday...
[KRILLIN] Rrgh!
[GOKU] Krillin, please! I know
this is the right thing to do!
You've got
to trust me!
But, the Saiyans killed
Yamcha... and Tien...
Chiaotzu... I can't
let him get away!
[GOKU] Don't do it, Krillin!
I know it seems like justice,
but it's not right!
If you strike him down,
it will only show
that we aren't any
better than he is!
It means that they've won,
no matter what! Be strong!
[GOKU] Don't forget, Krillin...
I'm a Saiyan, just like he is.
[GOKU] Thanks, Krillin...
That took a lot of
strength and courage...
I'm proud of you...
Goku... I sure hope you're
right about all of this...
I'd hate to think of what
might happen if he comes back
to try this again...
But, if he does...
We'll be ready for him,
and we'll stop him again!
You bet!
[thinking] I hope Goku
knows what he's doing.
I sure wouldn't
want for Earth
to have to face
that evil again...
Huh?
When I come back
to this planet...
You're all
going to suffer...
And when you beg
me for mercy...
I'll stare into your eyes as
I crush the life out of you.
[KRILLIN growling]
What? Huh?
[NARRATOR] After a long
and grueling battle,
Vegeta has finally
been defeated.
But the price of
victory was high...
Paid with the lives of Yamcha,
Tien, Chiaotzu and Piccolo.
Thus, one chapter in the
great adventure has ended,
and another is
about to begin,
as Goku and the others
must find a way
to bring their
friends back to life.
New dangers and powerful
new villains await,
as the story continues...
Next time on
Dragon Ball Z!