[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta launched
an all-out attack
against the
brutish Recoome,
but the Saiyan Prince's
strength was no match
for the might of
the Ginyu Force...
Fortunately, Krillin and Gohan
were standing by at the ready!
But even though
Vegeta was spared
the brunt of
Recoome's blast,
Krillin's counter-attack
had little effect.
Fool!
Hey! Jeice!
Burter!
Can I kill
this one, too?
[NARRATOR] And then the
unthinkable...
Krillin fell!
It's... all right... It's
time to face the facts.
The Dragon Balls
are gone...
[NARRATOR] Now, with Krillin and
Vegeta out of commission,
only one fighter remains to
challenge the evil Recoome.
You stay away!
I-I'm not gonna let you
hurt my friend any more!
[RECOOME] Let me get
this straight, little man.
You're gonna
stop me?
You think you're
tough, don't you?
Well, come on then,
let's see what you've got!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN growling]
[RECOOME guffaws]
[JEICE] Ugh. We should've
kept our turn...
[BURTER] Aw, let
Recoome have him.
I mean, it hardly
seems worth it now.
This kid won't put up
much of a fight on his own.
Gohan...
[VEGETA pants]
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN shouts]
[GOHAN grunting]
You had your
fun, kid?
[RECOOME grunts]
[GOHAN wailing]
[RECOOME guffaws]
Huh! Rah!
Comin' at ya!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN growls]
Masenko Haaaaa!
[RECOOME grunts]
Not bad...
Yeah! For a second there,
the kid's power went
up over 20,000!
[KRILLIN] Gohan...
[RECOOME chuckles]
[GOHAN gasps]
[RECOOME guffaws]
Aw, don't
sweat it, kid!
I don't mind gettin'
my hands dirty.
Not when there's
killing involved.
[RECOOME guffaws]
[GOHAN growls]
[RECOOME chuckles]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN screams]
[RECOOME shouts]
[GOHAN grunting]
[ChiChi]
Oh  no... Gohan!
[MRS. BRIEF] ChiChi?
Did you say something?
Is everything
all right, dear?
[ChiChi] I-It's my Gohan...
He's in trouble.
I just know it!
Ahh. Oh...
[ChiChi] He... He's
lost without me...
I have to
do something!
Don't worry
yourself too much.
I'm sure Gohan is
doing just fine.
After all, he's got my
Bulma to take care of him!
[MRS. BRIEF giggles]
[ChiChi] Dr. Brief!
I need that ship!
[DR. BRIEF] Oh, ChiChi!
Good, you're just in time!
I was just putting on
the finishing touches!
She's a beauty,
isn't she?
I had all the plans worked
out from the first one,
so putting this one
together was a snap!
I even managed to get
the cappuccino maker
installed this ti--
All that's left to do
now is test her out!
[CHICHI] Mommy's coming,
Gohan! Mommy's coming!
Just hold on!
I'm coming!
[DR. BRIEF] ChiChi? Maybe you'd
better let me just show you
how to work the
controls! ChiChi?!
C'mon you
bucket of bolts!
My son's in trouble!
Let's go already!
[DR. BRIEF] No, ChiChi! Wait!
It hasn't been tested yet!
You don't know
what you're doing!
[CHICHI grunting]
I'm coming, son!
[CHICHI screaming]
[DR. BRIEF] Well... Good thing
I installed those airbags.
Oh no! Mayday!
Mayday!
[CHICHI screams]
[RECOOME guffaws]
What's wrong?
No more fight left?
[GOHAN groaning]
[grunting]
[GOHAN growling]
Yaaah!
[RECOOME gasps]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN yells]
[RECOOME grunts,
GOHAN gags]
[GINYU] And one
more makes seven.
[FRIEZA] Once again,
you have more than
outdone yourself,
Captain Ginyu.
When I am the ruler
of the Universe,
your efforts will
be repaid tenfold.
I can already
see it now.
Thank you my loyal subject,
for a job well done.
It was my
pleasure, Frieza.
You know how much I enjoy
serving your lordship.
At last, I've
searched so long and
the Dragon Balls
are finally mine.
It's time to
make my wish...
[GINYU] Lord Frieza!
Allow me to honor you
by performing
the Dance of Joy!
[GINYU grunting]
Uh, Ginyu, if you
value your life, stop.
Oh... Yes, Lord.
[FRIEZA laughs]
Aw, did I hurt your feelings?
I'm so sorry... Get over it!
This is my moment of glory.
Don't spoil it for me.
You're right,
Lord Frieza.
I don't know what
came over me.
You have a
wish to make.
The Dance of Joy
can wait!
Now, Dragon Balls...
Grant my wish!
I want eternal life so
I can rule the universe!
[GINYU laughing]
[FRIEZA laughing]
[thinking]
What was that?
[thinking] Something's wrong...
I can feel it!
[thinking]
It's Elder Guru!
He's in
terrible danger.
The evil ones will be
coming for him soon!
[NAIL growling]
[thinking] I know Guru wanted
me to help the Earthlings...
But I cannot abandon him
in his hour of need!
[GOHAN yells]
[RECOOME] Huh, huh. Ouch!
[RECOOME chuckling]
[GOHAN grunting]
[RECOOME] Uh-oh!
[RECOOME chuckles]
[GOHAN grunting]
Dad... Where are you?
[GOHAN groans]
[GOHAN grunts]
[RECOOME guffaws]
He-Hey!
Whadda ya' know?!
Back for
more, huh?
[RECOOME chuckles]
[BURTER &amp; JEICE laugh]
[GOHAN panting]
I won't quit...
I have to keep fighting!
[GOHAN] My friends'... My
friends' lives depend on it!
Haa...
[RECOOME shouts]
[GOHAN grunts]
Hm?
[RECOOME grunts]
[blows landing,
RECOOME grunting]
GOHAN shouting]
[GOHAN growls]
Come on,
squirt!
Don't tell me that's
the best you've got!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN screams]
Uhhh...
[GINYU growling]
[FRIEZA] U-Uhh..
M-My wish...
Maybe it already came
true... I don't know.
Does it feel like you
have eternal life?
[FRIEZA] No... At least,
I... I-I don't think so...
Nothing's changed...
Why? What's wrong?!
Wait!
Here, it's yours!
Go ahead and take it!
It doesn't matter.
You'll never succeed!
Even if you do find
all seven balls,
you still won't be able
to make your wish...
[FRIEZA] Before I destroyed
his village and took
the second
Dragon Ball,
one of the elder Nameks
warned me this would happen.
I didn't think much
of it at the time.
People will say anything
when they're about to die.
But now it seems the old
geezer was telling the truth!
Urrgh... I can't
make my wish!
There must be some secret
to unlocking their power!
A password! A code!
Some sort of special ritual
to release the dragon
that only Nameks
would know!
I could scream!
Curses!
I have all seven Dragon Balls,
and they're worthless!
Now I need a Namek to
show me how to use them!
Check the Scouter,
Lord Frieza.
There's bound to be
one or two of them left.
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] Hmmm...
[FRIEZA] The rest of the Ginyu
Force is in that direction.
Perhaps Vegeta or
his new friends
can tell us what
we need to know.
Uhh?! It's best not to stop
the men once they get started.
I'm sure if we
keep looking...
Oh... Hey,
there we go!
There's still a small band
of Nameks in quadrant three.
You see? There's two of
them, due north.
And the third is
approaching from the East.
Somehow, they've managed to
avoid detection until now.
As usual, my men weren't
nearly as thorough
as they should have been
while searching the planet...
Normally, I'd be angry,
but in this case,
their incompetence has turned
out to be rather fortunate,
wouldn't you say?
Lord Frieza, just
give me one hour
and I'll find out
everything you need to know
about the
Dragon Balls!
I appreciate
your enthusiasm.
But I prefer to
handle this myself.
I've dealt with
enough Nameks now
that I know exactly
what buttons to push
to make them spill
their secrets...
You stay here,
Captain Ginyu.
I'm counting on you to
keep my Dragon Balls safe!
Right! You can
count on me, Lord!
I'll guard
them with my life!
Ha! Ready or not,
Nameks... Here I come!
[GOHAN grunting]
[panting]
Gohan...
[GOHAN] I have to
keep trying...
For Piccolo... For Yamcha...
Tien... Chiaotzu...
They're all
counting on me...
[RECOOME chuckles]
And I am not going
to let them down!
[GOHAN shouts]
[RECOOME] Ha, ha!
You missed me!
[GOHAN growls]
Now!
It's my tuuurn!
Recoooome
Bomber!
[RECOOME yelling]
[GOHAN shouts]
[RECCOME yelling]
[RECOOME yelling]
[RECOOME laughing]
[GOHAN screams]
Yoo-hoo!
[GOHAN grunts]
[screaming]
[GOHAN grunting]
[RECOOME] Hmmm...
Well, now...
Still alive, huh?
That's... enough...
Gohan... stop...
[GOHAN coughs]
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN] No... It's
not over yet...
I... won't... quit...
[GOHAN] Dad wouldn't give
up. Neither will I.
Well... Who's
the big man, huh?
Really, kid...
I've fought some stubborn
characters in my day...
But you...
You take the cake.
Now! Let Recoome
show you your doom!
Never! I'm not
gonna let you win!
[GOHAN screaming]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[grunting]
[RECOOME laughing]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[RECOOME] Hmph.
Haah.
[RECOOME laughs]
Gohan, no!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[JEICE chuckles]
Well, that's the
end of that.
I don't think that kid's
getting up this time.
How could he? Recoome
just snapped his neck!
[KRILLIN crying]
Bah! That little runt
was our last hope...
Damn! I should've known better
than to rely on a child!
[ChiChi] Gohan...?
[DR. BRIEF] Oh, good.
She's waking up!
[MRS. BRIEF] ChiChi, you
gave us such a scare!
Something's happened...
Oh, Gohan!
[CHICHI sobs]
[JEICE] Oy! Recoome!
Huh? What?!
[JEICE] Finish up your handiwork
so we can report back to Frieza!
[BURTER] Yeah, we don't
want to spend all day
watching you
have fun!
Let's get this
over with!
Hold your horses, this
will just take a second!
[BOTH gasp]
[JEICE] Wonder
who that is?
[BURTER] We're not
expecting anybody...
Maybe some Nameks
coming home from vacation?
[JEICE] Poor dopes!
They have no idea
what they're getting
themselves into!
[computer beeping]
[GOKU] It's time...
[NARRATOR] At long last, Goku
has arrived on Planet Namek!
And after his extensive
training in 100-times gravity,
he's ready to face
the challenges ahead.
But even with all of
his awesome strength,
will he be able to
save his friends?
Or is he already
too late?
Find out, in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!