[CELL laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
realizing that there
was no way to beat Gohan,
Cell decided to
go out with a bang.
[CELL] I'm going to
blow myself up now!
And I'm going to take
you with me! Ha, ha, ha!
So, say good bye to
your precious planet!
No, don't!
What?
Blow up the Earth?!
[NARRATOR] That's when Goku
took matters into his own hands.
Goodbye, my son...
[NARRATOR] With mere seconds
remaining, Goku had to act fast.
Using his Instant
Transmission Technique,
he transported Cell
to King Kai's planet,
just as the bloated beast popped
his top and blew up big time.
[CELL yells]
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] Cell was blown
to smithereens,
but his detonation also
had dire consequences for Goku.
King Kai's planet was
completely destroyed
along with everything on it.
[GOHAN] Daddy!
[NARRATOR] In a bold, final
move to save the Earth,
Goku had made
the ultimate sacrifice.
But there was little time
to mourn the fallen hero.
[PICCOLO] What was that?
[NARRATOR] From out of nowhere,
a giant storm cloud arose!
Could this be some freak act
of nature? I don't think so.
Forget the forecast, even I can
predict trouble when I see it.
No! It can't be!
What is that?!
He's... He's back!
[NARRATOR] There was
no denying the danger.
Gohan and the gang
could feel it in the air.
But there was little warning for
what was about to happen next.
[TRUNKS grunts]
[VEGETA gasps]
[NARRATOR] Somehow, Cell had
survived his own detonation.
The demented demon has come
back from the great beyond.
He's already blasted Trunks,
now he has his sights set
on the rest of the Z Warriors.
Can the good guys
get it together
before Cell picks
them off one by one?
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[TIEN growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[VEGETA gasps]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] What's wrong?
Surprised to see me?
[GOHAN] Cell, you monster!
Look what you did to Trunks!
[gasping, whimpering]
Oh no!
Cell has returned to Earth!
But... But the
Golden-Haired Challenger
is nowhere to be seen!
This is not a mirage, folks!
After being zapped away
by his renegade rival,
the monster has
come back for more!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
Oh... No one can hear me.
[VEGETA] What do you
want from us, Cell?!
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] Nothing.
I have everything I need now.
But he's... he's dead!
[VEGETA growls]
[GOKU] How can
Cell still be alive?
What do you mean, King Kai?
That's impossible!
I saw him blow up!
I can't explain it to you.
But somehow Cell
survived the blast!
Oh, come on!
You mean Cell can still
demolish the Earth?!
I'm afraid so.
Seems all you've managed
to do is destroy my planet!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Cell tricked me!
What's wrong, Dende?
It's Cell!
He's still alive!
Oh no!
It's true! He's somehow
regenerated himself!
Dende?
What can we do?
I just...
I-I don't know, Mr. Popo.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] You thought you'd
never see me again, didn't you?
Well, too bad! I'm alive!
But, I'm afraid I cannot
say the same thing for Goku.
Want to know how
I survived the blast?!
Well, it was
actually quite simple.
It is all in here.
It's part of my design.
Every cell has
a life of its own!
I can't die. It is impossible.
Even if I self destruct,
I will always come back.
[GOKU] Sorry,
this is the only place
I could think to
bring him, King Kai!
Well you could
have called first!
[CELL screams]
[CELL grunting]
[screaming]
[CELL] I don't remember
much after the explosion.
But somewhere amongst
the planetary debris,
the core of my being
still existed.
One living cell survived!
And that is all I
needed for my regeneration.
Soon, that single living cell
began to multiply into many.
It wasn't long before I became
conscious of my transformation.
I could feel every
part of my body growing,
crackling with
new life and energy.
My shapeless mass
began to sprout new limbs.
First my legs,
then my arms.
And in no time, my
whole body was restored.
[CELL gasps]
[CELL] At first,
I could hardly believe
that I had brought myself back
from the brink of extinction.
[CELL] That is when I realized
that each of my cells
must hold a memory
of my former self.
Each one programmed
to make me whole again.
[CELL grunting]
[CELL] And, to my great delight,
I had returned with
my complete power intact.
[CELL yells]
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] Causing my own
self destruction
was the best thing that ever
happened to me! I was reborn!
I must give Dr. Gero credit
for his brilliant design.
My complete power
had been restored
even though I
had lost Android 18.
My cells had tasted
the power and stored it away,
reawakening it
after the explosion
while my new body grew.
I also discovered that
I had the ability
to perform the Instant
Transmission Technique.
Somehow, during the blast,
my cells had absorbed
this knowledge from Goku.
So! There you have it!
You could say that
I am new and improved!
Goku failed and
so will all of you,
but I am willing to give you
another chance if you want!
[gasping]
[CELL] So, which one of you
cowards is the bravest?
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN yells]
Gohan! No!
[GOHAN]
You don't scare me, Cell!
[GOHAN growls]
Still won't give up.
Not a chance.
[CELL] Hmm... Really.
That's right! One thing
I learned from my father
is to never give up
even when the odds
are stacked against you!
If you're as powerful as you
say you are, then bring it on!
[GOHAN] Well, what are
you waiting for?
[CELL] You still have
a lot to learn, boy!
I'll make sure you
end up just like Goku!
[gasping]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[VEGETA gasps, growls]
[KRILLIN] Look! Trunks is
moving! He's still alive!
Trunks, hang on!
[YAMCHA] He's in really
bad shape! He might not make it!
Trunks... My son.
Goodbye, friends...
[GOHAN] Daddy!
[VEGETA thinking] Kakarot!
This is all your fault!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS screams]
Goku tried to
destroy me but failed.
Thanks to him, I am stronger
than I have ever been!
[GOHAN yells]
That's it!
Come on! This is
between you and me!
[thinking] How could I let
this happen to my son?!
He has sacrificed
everything for me,
and I have done
nothing but ignore him!
No! I won't
give up on him!
There is still time
to change things!
We never had a chance
to finish our fight!
[thinking] Cell has crossed
me for the last time!
He has tricked me in battle,
mocked my Saiyan ancestry!
But this! This time,
he's gone too far!
He will pay the ultimate price
for what he has done to my son!
[VEGETA yells]
[GOHAN gasps]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[CELL gasps]
[VEGETA growls]
Cell!
[VEGETA yells]
[CELL growls]
[CELL grunts]
[VEGETA growls]
[GOHAN gasps]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[yelling, whimpering]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA shouting]
[shouting continues]
[whimpering]
Wow! That guy is really giving
Cell everything he's got!
[ANNOUNCER growls]
[PICCOLO grunting]
Stop! Vegeta!
Man! What's up?
[KRILLIN] Talk about overdoing
it! What's he thinking?!
[VEGETA] I'll make sure he can't
put himself together again!
Cell! Come out! If you don't,
I'll blast you out of there!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA shouting]
[VEGETA] At last! It's over!
[GOHAN gasps]
[VEGETA gasps]
Wrong! It's over
when I say it's over!
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOHAN gasps]
I'd like to go home now!
Is this nightmare
ever gonna end?!
[VEGETA rasps]
And it's over, NOW!
[GOHAN screams]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] Gohan!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[CELL] Why would Gohan sacrifice
himself to save Vegeta?
Hmph! I will never understand
the ways of these Saiyans.
[CELL] Look at them!
They belong together!
They are both so weak!
[CELL] Hm?!
[GOHAN grunting]
[CELL chuckles]
Gohan! I told you
not to get in my way!
[CELL] I do hope you
are not planning
on continuing this fight?
I wouldn't want you to suffer.
[GOHAN growls]
No! Gohan!
[TIEN gasps]
No!
Vegeta, what have
you done?! You hothead!
You flying off the handle like
that is no way to help Trunks!
So, I see you are still
as stubborn as ever, Gohan.
Well, have it your way then.
Let's get this over with...
[thinking] I'm not giving up!
No way! This is for my dad!
He needs help!
Throw him a Senzu Bean!
But we don't have any left!
[PICCOLO growls]
Gohan is the
last chance we've got!
But he's hurt!
and Cell is so powerful!
This is so unfair!
Cell's sneak attack
on Trunks was bad enough
but now Vegeta
is in the same shape.
Without these two in the fight,
that means Gohan has to
face Cell all by himself!
[GOHAN gasps]
Gohan!
This is it! It ends here!
[CELL] First, I'll destroy you,
then your friends, and
then this worthless planet!
But before I do, I want
you to remember something.
I will live forever!
[ALL gasp]
[NARRATOR]
Since regenerating into
an indestructible force of evil,
there seems to be no
stopping the maniacal Cell.
But Gohan is determined
to stand until the end!
The young Super Saiyan has
faced overwhelming odds before,
but never this great.
Can he muster the strength to
stunt Cell's growth permanently?
Or have our young
hero's days come to an end?
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next Dragon Ball Z!