[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell took to the airwaves to
announce his malicious plan.
[CELL] Exactly nine
days from today...
bring me your best fighters
and I will face them one-by-one.
If I am not defeated,
the Earth belongs to me!
[NARRATOR] Viewers worldwide
could do little more than stare
into their television screens,
hoping to wake up
from this horrible dream.
But unfortunately,
the nightmare is real.
Today, on Dragon Ball Z!
[NARRATOR] The entire planet
is in a state of chaos
after Cell's televised
doomsday message.
In every city and every town,
people are gathering up
what they can and
fleeing in terror.
But with Cell on the watch,
don't they realize
that there's nowhere
left to run?
[horns honking]
Hey, what's the hold up?!
Let's move it!
Hurry up before we're all dead!
I've had it!
[DRIVER screaming]
What the--?!
[screaming continues]
[crashing]
[DRIVER whimpering]
[DRIVER grunts]
[bell clanging]
[CROWD screaming]
[OOLONG] Ahhh...
Oh, I wish there was someplace
we could hide until
this blows over!
B-But there aren't
any safe places left!
Chiotzu's right. From what
Cell said in his broadcast,
the entire planet is going to be
wiped out after the tournament!
I got it! We borrow
Bulma's ship, orbit the Earth
and then sit back
and watch the fireworks!
Oolong!
Yeah... I'd bet ol' Cell
would never think
to look for us up
in outer space!
Only a heartless soul would run
and leave his friends behind.
We're in this together.
[horns honking]
I just had to destroy it...
That was so dumb!
It's all my fault
that this happened!
[KRILLIN] I let Cell take her...
...and I made him complete!
[YAMCHA gasps]
I've gotta stop him!
[ROSHI] Krillin!
Stop right there!
[ROSHI] You know
good and well
that you are no match
for him, Krillin...
And I, for one, shall forbid
you to go! Understand?!
But if you still insist,
then enter his tournament
and face him there.
[YAMCHA] Hey, don't be so
hard on yourself, Krillin.
[ROSHI] Before we do anything,
we should talk to
Goku and Gohan.
If anyone is going to stop Cell,
it'll be one of those two.
Let's just hope
they've advanced enough
in their Super Saiyan training.
[TRUNKS] How much longer
are Goku and Gohan
going to be in there?
They still have three hours
left to finish off their year.
[VEGETA] I'm sure they'll
stay longer than that!
They'll do anything
they can to surpass me!
They are training so they
can beat Cell, not you, Vegeta.
And there are nine days left,
so you can afford to be patient.
Why don't you rest, Vegeta.
While I go in.
What a waste of time.
You don't actually expect to
become as strong
as a Saiyan, do you?
[PICCOLO growls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Fine, have your day.
But I plan to take the
remaining eight days for myself.
I wouldn't count on that.
Didn't you know you can
only spend two days inside?
Even the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber has its limits.
What?! You lie!
That's ridiculous!
How gullible do you think I am?!
[MR. POPO] But it's true.
After 48 hours the
entrance will disappear,
and you'll be trapped
inside for eternity.
But Father, there's
plenty of time!
We still have 23 hours left!
[gasping]
They must be done,
I can feel Goku's energy.
What? Why now?
That's not even a year.
[footsteps]
[VEGETA growls]
[footsteps continue]
Vegeta and Trunks?
I knew I sensed them, Gohan.
And I can still sense Cell too.
But he seems even stronger.
I can't believe...
how you've changed.
[GOKU] So, would someone fill us
in on what's been happening?
Yeah, sure.
Ohh, but before
you start talking,
I gotta get something
into my stomach.
Do you have anything
good to eat, Mr. Popo?
[MR. POPO sighs]
[TIEN laughs]
Well, at least he
hasn't changed at all.
[slurping &amp; chomping]
[GOKU] This is really
hitting the spot!
[GOHAN] You said it!
Goku, one question... okay?
[GOKU slurping]
Well, I mean, wasn't
there enough food
inside the Time Chamber?
[muffled] Oh, yer,
thurss luhssuv fhoo.
Bht neifer Goh'n urah cun cufk,
suffs brnuh rrghl
lahan tumm... shinz,
weff hurduh hum-cufk'd mehrl.
[TIEN chuckles in shock]
Okay, Goku, why don't
you try saying that
without your mouth full?
[BOTH] Hmmm?
[slurping]
--[GOKU gulps]
--[PICCOLO growls]
Disgusting...
What I was saying was, is that
Gohan and I can't cook very well
so it's been a
really long time since
we've had a good,
home-cooked meal.
I see.
[GOKU] I mean, seriously, guys,
us not cooking well
is an understatement!
There was this
time I asked Gohan
to fire me up a roast beef...
What is going on? They appear
to be Super Saiyans...
--[GOKU laughs]
--But they're acting so natural!
I must learn the full
extent of their new powers!
Thanks a lot, Mr. Popo!
Whew, that was excellent!
Huh...?
So, Trunks, why don't you
tell us what's been happening?
Huh? Yeah, sure, okay.
[horn honking]
[GIRL laughs]
Hello! Hello mister!
What are you looking at, honey?
Is there somebody out there?
Hmm...?
[MOTHER gasps]
[WOMAN screams]
[PASSENGERS screaming,
gasping]
Move it! Move it! Can't you
see he's right behind us?!
[MOTORIST B] Hurry up!
[MOTORIST A growls]
Huh...?!
[squealing]
So, where is everyone going?
[MOTORISTS whimper]
I have an idea.
Maybe I'll join you.
[screaming]
You forgot this.
[DR. BRIEF] Alright,
let me see...
was it the green wire,
or was it the red one?
No... hmm.
Maybe I'll try the white one.
Now where did I put my pliers?
Ahhh... here they--
No, that's not...
that's not the right set...
I don't understand...
If I would put these tools back,
I wouldn't have so much trouble
finding them...
Ahh... there.
[DR. BRIEF continues to mumble]
Look at this, Dad.
I downloaded the
memory of Android 16
and it's loaded
with Goku's data!
[DR. BRIEF] Interesting!
[BULMA] He's got everything!
Fighting records,
his common techniques,
even his home address!
How strange!
Yeah, the only conclusion
that makes sense
is that Android 16
was designed
for the sole purpose
of destroying Goku.
But it doesn't seem like
he's after Goku at all...
Or maybe the right opportunity
just hasn't
presented itself yet.
Huh...?
Well, his circuitry is
too complex to really say.
However, he doesn't
look too evil.
[DR. BRIEF] And as I understand,
the only aggressive move he's
made has been against Cell.
That's true.
[DR. BRIEF] It really raises
profound questions about
the nature of
artificial intelligence.
Despite all of
Dr. Gero's programming,
this android could
still make a choice.
Yeah... well, I'm glad
he chose to be on our side
at the tournament,
because once we get
finished fixing him up,
he'll be one of the
strongest players we've got!
[GOKU] Hmm... So that's it!
A tournament, huh? I gotta
say it sounds interesting.
What? Interesting?
Hey, Mr. Popo, do ya still
have the clothes I left here?
Sure, I do.
They're somewhere.
I even washed them for you.
Hey, thanks. I appreciate that.
I'm sure my mother would make
you some new Saiyan armor
if you asked her.
Nah, this'll do fine. I want
to fight as an Earthling.
Piccolo, can I have a new
outfit just like yours?
You were my first teacher.
Yeah, kid, it'll make
you look really sharp.
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Wow!
Thank you! It's awesome!
[GOKU] You look great, Gohan.
--Okay.
--Huh?
Kakarot, you think
you can beat Cell now?
Couldn't really tell ya.
I haven't seen him since he
absorbed 18 and transformed.
I'll have to go check him out.
Ahh, Goku.
Yeah, that's right.
Right here, is where the fate of
the universe will be determined.
So what do you think?
[GOKU] I don't know,
seems kind of puny
if it's supposed to
decide all that,
wouldn't you say?
[CELL chuckles]
[GOKU] You're not
the first person
to try and rule the universe
with a sword of injustice.
They all failed,
and so will you.
[thunder crashing]
[GOKU] I've spent months
preparing for the day
I'd face you in
your final form.
I've come a long way, Cell.
So have I.
[PUAR whimpers]
[CHIAOTZU whimpers]
[OOLONG gasps]
What's going on out there?
Is... all that energy
I'm sensing from Cell?
No. There's someone with him,
someone almost as strong...
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL] Goku?!
Huh...?
[KRILLIN laughs]
It must be him!
He's finished, guys!
He's finally out of the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber!
I'll be your first opponent.
So leave everyone out of this
until we meet in the ring.
Agreed?
[CELL] Hmph.
You will pay for your crimes.
Huh?
Well then, Goku.
You've just made my little
match even more interesting.
[TRUNKS] So, what did
you think, Goku?
To be honest, Trunks,
he's become a whole lot
stronger than I thought he'd be!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOKU] Of course, I won't
really know how tough he is
until I see him fight, but...
Well, if I were
to fight him right now,
I'm pretty confident that
he'd beat me into the ground.
Hm?!
[BOTH gasp]
[TRUNKS] Oh, okay.
I get it, Goku.
I understand.
He can still can use
the Hyperbolic Time
Chamber once more.
There is still
plenty of time left
and we've decided
to go in first.
Then Vegeta,
who wants to go alone.
That's because I
don't want any of you to
interfere with my training.
Well, I... I've decided
not to go in because
I don't think I'd be
a worthy opponent.
Trunks will be next.
Followed by Goku and Gohan.
You two will be last.
[GOKU] Gohan and I
don't need a turn.
What?!
There's only nine days left,
so I think we'll just
train outside 'til then.
You're not serious?!
[NARRATOR] Goku wants
to train in the outer world.
But will it be enough for
the final battle against Cell?
Find out on the
next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!