[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku was fully recovered and
was finally ready for action.
ChiChi could only
stand by helplessly
and wonder if she would ever
see her precious Goku again.
Saving the world is a tough job,
but somebody's got to do it.
Piccolo wasn't wasting
any time doing his part.
Marvelously strong after
being reuniting with Kami,
the Super Namek found
himself at the forefront
of the battle
against the androids.
[PICCOLO gasps]
Well done.
Impressive light show.
[NARRATOR]
Amazingly enough,
a much greater threat
than the androids
was lurking in a city nearby.
Ah, yes, perfect! Piccolo
must be fighting Android 17,
I can feel his energy signal.
Wonderful!
This is going to be
far less difficult
than I had ever imagined.
[NARRATOR] It seems that Cell
is not far from absorbing
Androids 17 and 18 and
completing his evolution!
Already a being
of horrible strength,
can anyone stop Cell from
carrying out his deadly mission?
Find out today!
It's a shame that you
insist on getting in our way.
Our mission has
nothing to do with you.
It's Goku that we're after.
Terminating your life is not
something that we wish to do.
It doesn't make sense
for you to die out here
in the middle of nowhere when we
have no interest in killing you.
Why don't you just
tell us where Goku is
and then leave, unharmed.
It's the only
logical thing to do.
[PICCOLO]
Well, soon you'll realize
that the people on this
planet aren't logical at all.
Funny thing is,
they've rubbed off on me.
Fine. I'll make you
tell us where he is.
Now, how's that sound?
Bad move. But at least
you're not boring.
[ANDROID 17] After all, I rather
enjoy not adhering to logic.
--[ANDROID 17] Haah!
--[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[popping]
Well, your speed is excellent.
But your punches are
lacking in stopping power.
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[PICCOLO]
Yeah, Goku punches harder.
But that's impossible. No way.
I see. You're just
bluffing, aren't you?
Well, I'm not buying it.
No mere mortal
can equal me in power.
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[ANDROID 17] You can't
keep this up. You'll tire out.
[PICCOLO]
And you're not perfect.
You'll might make a
mistake before that happens.
[ANDROID 17] You're just
a flesh and bone creation.
17! Don't underestimate him.
He's a lot stronger
than we originally thought.
[GOHAN]
Piccolo...
Hey, Dad. Can he win?
I don't think so, Son.
But, if he can hold on
he might... live.
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Huh?
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 18] Hmm...?
[BOTH yell]
[grunting]
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[ANDROID 17 &amp; PICCOLO grunt]
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[yelling continues]
[ANDROID 18] Hm? Hmm...
[low rumbling]
[ANDROID 18] We're going to run
out of islands at this rate.
Men, hah. They just have
to destroy everything.
[KRILLIN]
This is terrible!
Being on the sidelines is
harder than actually fighting!
I can't take it!
Especially with the
smoke and the explosions
and the whole shebang
right in front of our faces!
Am I the only one that
this is getting to or what?
[TIEN]
No way! I'm going crazy!
Darn! Come on you guys, there's
got to be something we can do!
[YAMCHA]
Look! We have our orders!
We've got to stick to the plan!
It's for Piccolo's
safety as well as ours!
[KRILLIN] Huh?!
[YAMCHA] If they get
a hold of one of us,
they'll have Piccolo
right where they wanted him!
It's horrible, you guys!
[TIEN] I know!
That's what I'm saying!
Krillin, is there
something wrong?
Yeah, more bad news!
It's... Cell!
What? Cell?
[ROSHI]
Oh, now I can feel it!
Man! I can't!
[TIEN gasps]
[YAMCHA] Oh, yeah!
I feel it now too!
Oh, my gosh!
Wicked, man! Whoa!
[ROSHI] Oh, dear!
Boys, I'm afraid this is
some vintage bad stuff!
I've never felt
anything like it!
[KRILLIN]
Aye yai yai...
What a grand day!
The day that I become complete!
Just the thought
of it makes me tingle!
[CELL laughs]
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
[DR. BRIEF]
Now, now! There, there!
Your mother
is working, Trunks!
Look at Grandpa, Boy!
That's funny. That one
almost always works!
Hey! Mayday, Bulma! Help!
Just a second, Dad! Please!
This should do it!
I'm almost there!
[DR. BRIEF]
I don't think I can take this
much longer, honey!
I'm exhausted!
Hey! Come on! I haven't
slept for forty-eight hours!
What do you think
about that, huh?!
Well, but... right...
[BULMA]
Nice, Dad!
[YAJIROBE] Well, I'll tell you
what I have to say about that.
Take care of your kid.
He's driving us all nuts.
Forty-eight hours of torture.
Look, no offense, little
amigo. I don't blame you.
I'd be doing the
same thing if I were you.
[BULMA]
There! That's it!
Ta-daaa! I did it!
All finished, guys!
Ahh! It's so rare to
find beauty and genius
all wrapped into
one tidy package!
Well, isn't it?!
That's great, hon!
Just take him!
Oh, my! Thank goodness!
Great work, hon! You did it!
Thanks, Dad! If it
works, I should be able
to stop the androids
with the push of a button!
[YAJIROBE] Awesome!
[DR. BRIEF]
That's my little girl!!
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 17 snarls]
[BOTH grunt]
[ANDROID 17] Piccolo was
supposed to be nothing to us.
Why the change?
We didn't even think that
Goku would be this strong.
[thinking] Fascinating...
[thinking] Alright. Come on,
then. Yes. Yes! That's it!
Perfect!
[ANDROID 18] 16, check that out.
Something's brewing down there.
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
How rude.
[YAMCHA] Piccolo's on the
move again, isn't he?
[TIEN] Yeah! Definitely!
It feels like Cell
is hot on their trail!
You know it! That hideous
monster isn't wasting any time!
He wants to absorb
those two androids!
And, the thing is, Piccolo's
leading him right to them!
Man!
[CHICHI] Hey! Telephone, guys!
Collect call! It's Bulma!
[YAMCHA] Don't accept.
Oh, come on, guys.
It's urgent!
She's figured out a way
to disable the androids!
What?
[ALL] Accept the charges!
I heard all that!
Well, I guess I'll still
let you guys use the remote
I invented that disables
the androids' circuits!
But only if Mister Loud-Mouth
Don't-Accept-the-Charges Yamcha
agrees to give
yours truly a foot massage!
[KRILLIN] Gosh,
I don't know, Bulma!
Well, that's the deal! So!
You can take it or leave it!
She knows that I can't
stand rubbing her feet!
Hey! You've got a deal!
But we're running
out of time, Bulma!
Piccolo's already
fighting the androids,
and Cell is on
his way to the battlefield!
[BULMA] Right! I'm on my way!
That's great! If we
can destroy the androids,
then there's no way that Cell
can complete his evolution!
[YAMCHA] Ha! Leave it to
Bulma to figure out
how to get rid of the most
powerful fighters in the world
with the push of a button!
[TIEN] Yeah!
[YAMCHA] I'm telling you, bro.
[KRILLIN thinking] It
happened so fast!
But it seemed to
last forever! Wow...
What's wrong?
[KRILLIN] Uh, wrong?
Nothing's wrong! Why?
[BULMA] Guys, I'm leaving Trunks
here! This is an emergency! Hey!
Think again! No way! You
hear that? That's an emergency!
You're the one who
made him cry, you dope!
Now let go!
Whoa! Daddy!
It's Cell! Isn't it?
He's heading
for Piccolo, isn't he?
[GOKU] Yes, Son! I'm afraid so!
And... Son, I know how you feel.
I'd much rather it be
me down there than Piccolo.
[GOKU] Come on, Vegeta!
Please! Hurry!
Out of all the
battles I've been in
this is the hardest thing
that I've ever done by far...
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO pants]
[PICCOLO growls]
--[ANDROID 17 yells]
--[PICCOLO grunts]
[BOTH growl]
[PICCOLO growls,
ANDROID 17 yells]
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 17 growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[ANDROID 17 shouts]
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[grunting]
--[ANDROID 17] Haah!
--[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] Hrrgh!
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO] Not bad for a machine.
Especially an early
prototype like yourself.
[ANDROID 17] You don't know
what you're talking about!
I am the ultimate android! There
are no improvements to be made!
Now I get it. You're playing
with my head, aren't you?
Yes! You're trying to make
me think that you're stronger!
When, in fact, you're
the one who's actually
getting worn down!
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
[ANDROID 17] This game is much
more difficult than I thought,
but it fascinates me to no end!
I'm learning a lot
from you, Piccolo.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[CELL] Delightful!
What a momentous occasion!
A day for the
history books, to be sure!
The completion of my being will
mark the dawning of a new age!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Hello, Piccolo!
You recognize me, don't you?
Thank you for
bringing 17 and 18 here!
It pleases me greatly!
You should feel fortunate
to have played a part
in the events leading
up to my completion!
[CELL chuckles]
[GOKU thinking]
Come on, Vegeta! Hurry!
[NARRATOR] Cell has arrived
to absorb Androids 17 and 18
and complete his
dreadful evolution!
Does Android 16,
the silent giant,
have the power to stop him?
And why is Piccolo the
only one sweating bullets?
Don't the androids
realize who Cell is
and what he intends to do?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!