[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Goku mixed up
Captain Ginyu's plans
to swap bodies with Vegeta.
[NARRATOR] As a result,
Goku got his body back.
[GINYU] What?
[NARRATOR] The beaten and
battered Captain Ginyu
wasn't ready to give up yet.
He knew he had one more chance
to switch bodies with Vegeta.
[NARRATOR] But as he tried,
Goku foiled his plans once more.
And as a result, Captain Ginyu
ended up in the body of a frog.
I've got my body back!
[NARRATOR] Battling had taken
it's toll on Goku's body,
and he was put into a
special recuperating capsule
by Krillin, Gohan, and Vegeta to
restore his Super Saiyan powers.
[NARRATOR] At the spaceship,
Vegeta showed signs that
something may be bothering him,
but what?
I might run into Frieza,
but I guess I'm gonna
have to take that chance.
Besides, Gohan, without
the correct password
we're never going to get our
wish from the Dragon Balls!
I'll go with you!
No, you stay here
and look after Goku.
[NARRATOR] As Goku recuperated,
Krillin left to try and get
the password from Guru.
Will Krillin return safely
with the Dragon Ball password
or does the evil Frieza
have other plans
for our heroic friends?
Find out today!
I sure hope this
new armor works.
I'll bet you almost anything,
Mom and Piccolo would
be surprised to see
me wearing a
Saiyan uniform!
[GOHAN chuckles]
You know, I really feel
indestructible in this!
Super Gohan!
Get ready to meet the universe's
most powerful Saiyan good guy!
What do you think you're doing?
So kid, what's taking
your bald-headed buddy
so long with that
stupid password?
Wait. He'll show.
[VEGETA] He'd better!
[VEGETA chuckles]
In the meantime, you
better keep your eyes
on those Dragon Balls,
'cause if we lose those, I'm
going to be totally pissed.
Well, I think it's
time for a little nap!
You're taking a nap?
[VEGETA] Well, with you
wearing that new armor,
I feel real safe!
[VEGETA laughs]
Gotta hurry. Not much time.
I just hope Goku and Gohan
are gonna be alright
with Vegeta back there!
And then there's Frieza.
If he ever discovered that
I was out here by myself,
then I would be a
goner for sure.
[KRILLIN] I can't waste a
second getting to Guru's!
I just hope I can get
to Krillin and the others
in time to tell them
what the password is.
I found them!
[DENDE] Oh no, there's
something fishy here...
There's no sign of them!
Yaah!
Oh no! Krillin!
[DENDE] No, it can't beee!
Krillin! Nooo!
Huh? This isn't Krillin!
This is strange! What
could've happened here?
[VEGETA] Get well, Kakarot.
You'll need your strength
to defend against Frieza.
And later to
defend against me...
[VEGETA grunts]
I think I overdid it
a little bit...
I figure it should only
take about a half an hour
to get my strength back...
Let's see...
[VEGETA] A Super Saiyan
does need his rest...
[VEGETA] I can hardly wait until
the Dragon grants my wish!
[GOHAN] I can't believe
he left me here by myself.
What if Frieza shows up?
[NAIL pants]
[FRIEZA] I must say, Nail,
you are one pathetic warrior.
Do you really think you
stand a chance against me?
[FRIEZA] Might I
suggest you give up now
while you're still breathing
and simply tell me the password?
Hmmm...?
[FRIEZA] Oh well, suit yourself.
[NAIL] Haaah!
Wha--?!
You really are starting
to bore me, my dear friend.
[NAIL gasps]
[NAIL growls]
[FRIEZA] As you well know by
now, you can never defeat me.
So my question is:
Why are you still trying?
And if you don't tell me,
maybe I'll just have
to beat it out of Guru.
Is that what you want?
It doesn't make
any difference to me.
One way or another,
I will get that password!
[NAIL gasps]
Huh--?
[NAIL groans]
[FRIEZA] So, just to
set the ground rules,
that was my last warning.
Either you divulge what I want,
or you will never get up again!
You truly are pathetic!
[NAIL chuckles]
You know, I think it's time I
let you in on a little secret.
Huh?
[NAIL] Our little
diversion worked perfectly.
[NAIL chuckles]
Yep. By now, Dende
has given the password
to the people from Earth!
What?! I don't... Ah!
Mark my words, I'm not
finished with you yet!
[NAIL chuckles]
Ginyu Force, this is
Frieza, come in, over!
What?! No!
This can't be!
Where are my soldiers?!
Why aren't they showing
up on my scouter?!
There's no way Vegeta and
those miserable little punks
could take down the
entire Ginyu force!
If they're sleeping on the
job, I will make them pay!
Idiots! They better not
have let those imbeciles
near the Dragon Balls!
Because the only one allowed
to make a wish is Frieza!
[GURU] Oh, it's all my fault...
I should have given the password
to Krillin and his friend
when they were here...
And now I feel so bad for
putting Nail through all that.
If only I had known!
[GURU coughs]
Please! Please, Dende!
You must hurry!
I don't have much time left
and I know Frieza
is right behind you.
Where are you?!
[DENDE] Krillin! Gohan!
Man, I wonder when Krillin's
coming back. I hope he's okay.
It shouldn't have taken
him nearly this much time
just to fly over to
Guru's and back.
Yeah, I sure hope he
at least gets back here
before Frieza shows up.
[GOHAN] Well, I shouldn't
worry too much,
because with this
cool fighting suit,
I could probably hold of
Frieza for a while by myself.
I mean, I think I could...
[FRIEZA growls]
Huh? What?
I've gotta a funny
feeling I'm not alone.
[KRILLIN] I better
check this out!
[KRILLIN] Wait a second!
That's Dende!
Hey!
Huh?
[DENDE screams]
[KRILLIN laughs]
It's only me, Krillin! I'm just
wearing a Saiyan uniform!
Ah! It is you, Krillin!
--What a relief!
[GINYU grunting]
[GINYU screams]
[grunting continues]
Huh...?
Ribbit! Ri-Ribbit!
[GINYU chuckles]
A frog? Hmm...
[GINYU whistles]
Hold on...
Hey, I know who you are!
You're the frog that
took over my dad's body
and then tried to do
away with him, aren't you?
Ribbit! Ribibibi!
[GINYU chuckles]
Uh, ribbit? Ribbit.
[GOHAN chuckles]
Now say good night, Froggy!
[GINYU] Woah-ho-ho!
[GINYU grunting]
[GOHAN laughs]
You can hop, but you can't hide!
[FEMALE FROG]
Ribbit... ribbit...
Ribbit... Ribbit...
[GINYU whimpers]
[KRILLIN laughs]
Man, is it good to see you!
And your timing couldn't
have been any better
because we've managed to
find all seven Dragon Balls!
But the problem we're having is
that we don't know the password
and so we can't make our wish.
That's exactly what Guru said.
That's why he sent me
to find you guys so I
could tell you the password
and you could make your wish!
That's great! So, you
gonna tell me what it is?
It's in Namek,
and you probably
wouldn't understand it
even if I told it to you.
In Namek, huh?
Well, I gotta tell ya,
if Guru had told us that
when we were there,
he sure would have saved
us all a lotta trouble!
[DENDE] At the time, Guru didn't
think you'd be able to collect
all seven Dragon Balls.
Well, that explains it...
[DENDE] Hey, we'd better
step on it, Krillin!
I mean, if we don't,
Frieza might show up.
before we even get a
chance to use the password!
Right! Let's get moving.
Huh? I think someone's coming!
[GOHAN] Maybe it's Krillin!
Man, I sure hope so!
I can sense them, but I
can't make out who they are!
It is Krillin! All right!
[KRILLIN] Look, it's Gohan!
[DENDE] And he's alright!
[GOHAN laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
Krillin! I'm so happy
you made it back okay!
[KRILLIN] What? You didn't
think I could do it?
Oh, and you do remember
this guy, don't you?
[GOHAN] Of course. Do you happen
to know the password, Dende?
Yes!
Hey, why isn't Vegeta here?
Wasn't he supposed to be helping
you protect the Dragon Balls?
Where is he?!
[GOHAN] Oh, yeah. Vegeta...
He went inside the ship and
said he was going to take a nap.
But that was almost an hour ago.
Ahhh, this is perfect.
All we have to do now is
gather up the Dragon Balls,
but we gotta be quiet because
we don't wanna wake up Vegeta!
Then we bring the
Balls to this side,
so if Vegeta does wake up, it'll
take him time to get to us.
--[GOHAN] Right.
--[DENDE] Right.
[KRILLIN] Good! Let's go!
[KRILLIN] Yeah! We did it!
Phew...
We're all counting
on you, Dende!
Yes!
[FRIEZA growling]
[GOHAN gasps]
[KRILLIN laughs]
Hey! Quiet, Krillin! I think
I sense someone coming!
And he's closing in fast!
[DENDE &amp; KRILLIN gasp]
Ah, i-it's Frieza!
Dende, you had better
use that password now
before it's too late!
Takkarapt pop
porunga pupiritparo!
Are you sure that's
the right password?
Um, Dende? I thought you
said you knew what it was.
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN gasp]
They're glowing!
Krillin, look at the sky!
Yeah, I think that means
they're working now.
What's happening?! Why has
the sky turned so dark?
[ALL grunting]
[KING KAI] Do you feel it?!
Finally, their wish
will come true!
[CHIAOTZU] Yay, alright!
They did it! Yippee!
[CHIATZU laughs]
Isn't this exciting, Tien?
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[DENDE whimpers]
[ALL whimpering]
Oh, man... He's... He's huge!
Bigger than anything I've
ever seen in my whole life!
Are you sure this
is the Dragon?
[DENDE] Yes, Gohan.
His name is Porunga and in
Namek it means "Dragon of Love."
But to be honest,
this is the first time
I've ever had a
chance to see him!
You have collected
all seven Dragon Balls.
And now as it is written,
think wisely and I will
grant you three wishes
within my power!
Wait, three? Did say
three wishes, Dende?
That's right. Now, please,
hurry and make your wishes!
Oh yeah! Did you
hear that Gohan?
We get to make two extra wishes!
That's awesome! So what do
you think we should wish for?
[NARRATOR] The Dragon
has been summoned!
And our heroes now have
three wishes to make.
But what will those
wishes be used for?
Will our heroes accomplish
what they set out to do?
Will Vegeta or Frieza arrive in
time to change their plans?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!