[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
The battle between
Cell and Gohan raged on.
And Gohan demonstrated
that his powers
had transcended those
of any other Super Saiyan.
[CELL] Don't get too confident!
For I have yet to
show you, young warrior,
what I'm truly capable of!
Can it.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR] Confronted
with an opponent
of overwhelming strength,
Cell was forced to reveal
the full extent of his power.
Until now, the evil android
had been holding back,
but against Gohan's
awesome abilities,
he had no choice but
to pull out all the stops.
Cell expected to see the
fresh-faced challenger
turn and run, but the
gifted young Super Saiyan
stood his ground!
[CELL chuckles]
[grunting]
[NARRATOR] Cell attacked
with a flurry of fisticuffs
that flattened Gohan,
but the young fighter
was unphased by his
fearsome foe's attack.
He returned fire with an iron
fist that sent Cell reeling.
[CELL grunts]
[NARRATOR]
Gohan was unstoppable.
With just two punches,
the heroic youth put
Cell's lights out.
[CELL] He only... had two
punches that made contact!
Gohan just won it all!
[NARRATOR] Now Gohan has Cell
right where he wants him.
[CELL] Why am I so damaged?
[NARRATOR] Will Gohan finally
put an end to the Cell Games?
[CELL growls]
[KRILLIN] Why doesn't Gohan
just finish Cell off?!
Hey! Have you fixed
that camera yet?
Not yet, boss!
Well, at least try
to fix the microphone!
My fans don't want to miss
the battle of the century!
[MR. SATAN] Wow,
I can't believe this kid!
[CELL growls]
[CELL gasps]
[CELL] You are as
foolish as your father!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] It's time for you
to learn some respect!
[CELL growls]
[growling continues]
[CELL grunting]
[CELL yells]
NOW FIGHT ME!
[GOHAN yells]
[CELL grunts]
[CELL grunting]
[CELL] I will not be
humiliated by a child!
This has gone far enough! I'm
tired of playing these games!
[CELL growls]
[thinking] This can't be
happening! I am complete!
It is impossible for a
Saiyan child to defeat me!
I am the ultimate fighter!
I have no equal!
Yet somehow
this one is different!
Very well. If I must prove
myself once again then so be it!
But this will be the last time!
[CELL growls]
[growling continues]
[CELL yells]
[CELL grunts]
[KRILLIN gasps] Look out!
Gohan!
[CELL] Destructo Discs!
[CELL yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
[CELL gasps]
What?!
Whoa! He caught them!
He caught the discs!
Impossible!
Gohan...
[thinking] That's it, Gohan.
Use your training.
[GOHAN growls]
[yelling]
You little fool! I will
show you what true power is!
[CELL yells]
[CELL] Special Beam Cannon!
[CELL laughs]
Now what will you do?!
Watch and learn.
[GOHAN grunts]
[gasping]
Curse you!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] Rapid Fire!
[CELL grunting]
What? He's still standing!
[thinking] Those blasts
went right through him!
It's impossible!
[MR. SATAN] This kid is gold!
Yeah! That's it!
[ALL] Huh?
[PIIZA] What's "it"?
This kid's has some talent.
I've decided to
take him under my wing.
[gasping]
But, Maestro, what about us?
We paid you to train us!
What?! You two idiots
aren't worth my time!
[BOTH] Hey! That hurts!
Hey, what a
great idea, Hercule!
You get that kid on contract
and he'll bring in lots
of money to your Dojo!
I hadn't thought of that...
Uh, listen, Mr. Satan...
I really hate to say this,
but honestly, who
are you trying to fool?
It's obvious to everyone here
that the kid is far
more skilled than you!
[MR. SATAN growls]
What?! Come on,
are you for real?!
That kid is an amateur!
Oh, sure, he's got talent,
but he needs help!
If he trains hard enough,
he could be as good as me!
Uh-huh...
[LIONEL groans]
Look, Krillin!
The tables have turned on Cell!
I think Gohan's got him!
Yeah, it's unbelievable! Wow!
Do you think he
can beat him this time?
He will.
[CELL whimpers]
[GOHAN] What are you
so afraid of, Cell?
Isn't this what you wanted?
[GOHAN] I warned you.
I told you what would happen
if you pushed me too far!
But you didn't listen.
You forced me to
awaken my hidden power!
And now that you've
seen it, you're afraid.
Because you know that
I'm going to destroy you!
[CELL gasps]
[CELL screams]
[KRILLIN] All right! I think
Cell is chickening out!
[CELL] Kaa...
Meeh...
Haa...
No... Don't do it, Cell!
Meeh...
[CELL laughs]
Here you go!
Let's see you try and stop this!
I'm going to blow up the Earth!
And there's nothing you can do!
Gohan! Get out of there!
He's gonna do it!
[CELL] HAAA!
[GOKU] NOOO!
[gasping]
No! Not like this!
[GOHAN] Kaa... meeh... haaa...
meeh...
HAAAA!!
[CELL] What have you done?!
No!
[CELL grunting]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[CELL growls]
[CELL screaming]
[CELL screams]
[CELL] I can't stop it!
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA thinking]
How could Gohan
have that much
power inside him?!
He released a bigger
Kamehameha Wave than Cell!
He should be exhausted!
What's his secret?!
[grunting]
[KRILLIN] Man,
who would have thought
getting rid of Cell
would be such a blast.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
No! Cell is still alive!
There's no way he could be!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, that energy wave
swallowed him up completely!
[thinking] It looks
like Piccolo's right.
Gohan might
have slowed him down,
but he is still very much alive.
[CELL growls]
Heh...
[thinking] Gohan's power has
grown far beyond mine.
When were training in
the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
I knew he had hidden strengths,
but I never knew he
would ascend to this level...
[GOKU &amp; GOHAN grunting]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[GOKU thinking]
Each time we trained,
his energy level increased,
and I saw his
fighting techniques improve.
It wasn't long before
he was as good as me.
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU thinking] Even when I
knew he couldn't take any more
he refused to give up!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU chuckles]
Let's call it a day.
We practiced for
twenty hours already!
Come on, Gohan I think
it's time for a break.
[GOHAN] Wait, Dad!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN] Let's keep going!
[GOKU thinking]
Watching Gohan that day,
I realized that there were
hidden depths to his power
I would never
even begin to fathom!
[GOKU thinking]
And that's when I knew!
If anyone was going to
have a chance at beating Cell,
it would be him.
[GOHAN yells]
[thinking] I'm proud
of you, Gohan.
You've mastered
your powers.
Now go show Cell
what you're made of!
[TIEN] Hey, what's wrong?
What's he waiting for?!
No! He's a boy!
There's no way that little
brat can be so strong!
[PICCOLO gasps]
Hey! If he waits too long,
Cell will regenerate himself!
[ALL] Huh?!
Remember, he has
my cells inside him!
Gohan!
You've got to take Cell down
now before he can regenerate!
Take him down now?
No, I think I'll wait.
I'm going to let him
suffer for a little while.
Wait? No, Gohan...
[PICCOLO] He's running
out of time, Goku!
Yeah!
[CELL grunts]
Gohan! Listen to me! You've
got to get him! Do it now!
We all know you have the
power! It's time to use it!
[CELL grunts]
[CELL growls]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[CELL pants]
I... am whole!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] You wretched child!
How dare you?!
HOW DARE YOU?!!
[CELL yells]
[CELL roaring]
[CELL snarls]
[KRILLIN] Oh no! Cell's
back to his old evil self!
Boy! You won't defeat me!
A worthless Saiyan like
you can't compete with me!
I am invincible!
And now I will make you pay!
[CELL growls]
[yelling]
[CELL growling]
[CELL grunting]
Look! Cell might have power,
but he can't catch Gohan!
He's too bulky! His size
is slowing him down!
[CELL yelling]
[CELL grunts]
[CELL] You're not a boy...
You're a monster!
[CELL whimpers]
[CELL grunts]
[CELL garbles]
[CELL] What have you
done to me...?
[CELL rasps]
Hey! Look!
Looks like something's
happening to Cell!
He's sick!
It won't be long now.
Huh...?
His life force
is getting weaker...
And in a moment,
Cell's complete power
will have left him for good!
What? How do you know that?
[PICCOLO] Watch and
you'll see what I mean.
What?! What's that?!
[BOTH gasp]
[TIEN] Look...
it's Android 18!
I don't believe it! She was
inside Cell the whole time!
What...? But it can't be!
I thought she was a goner!
But if she's free,
then what does that mean?
The end of Cell!
[thinking] I hope
you're right, Piccolo...
[CELL retching]
[CELL] I'll get you for this!
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR] Now that
Gohan has freed Android 18
from the belly of the beast,
Cell's power is fading fast.
Gohan knows that with
his Super Saiyan strength
he could finish Cell off easily.
But what is he waiting for?!
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!