[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
the citizens cleared the
streets as the boys in blue
unloaded on the
swooping giants above!
Don't shoot!
They're just trying
to get their baby back!
[VIDEL]
Come here, little guy!
I found him!
[NARRATOR] And when the greedy
circus promoter went berserk,
Saiyaman had to knock
the giant dinosaur out,
so he could arrange
for a peaceful reunion,
and the arrest of the
trigger-happy promoter!
[GOHAN] He'll be just fine!
Wait and see!
[NARRATOR] But just when he
thought the trouble was over,
Gohan ran straight
into an ambush!
My gosh, isn't
that funny! Yeah!
I saw Saiyaman get
scratched in the same spot!
And that's exactly
who you are! Mr. Saiyaman!
Yikes! Busted!
I can't believe it!
The secret identity of
Saiyaman is public knowledge!
[NARRATOR] That's right!
The cat's out of the bag!
Gohan is Saiyaman!
And now he's at Videl's mercy!
I wouldn't exactly say that
it was public knowledge!
Only I know!
But maybe I should schedule
a press conference,
what do you think?
[PASSENGERS screaming]
[MAN 1] Oh, my gosh!
It's gonna crash!
[ANCHORMAN]
And there you have it, folks,
the cries of horror on
Flight 336 were turned into
shouts of joy as the
disaster over downtown
was narrowly
averted by Saiyaman--
the remarkable hero
who seems to have
made a home in our fair city!
No one knows who he is
or where he came from!
Channel Ten's Nick Hornby
is at the scene!
How amazing!
Great Saiyaman,
there seems to be no limit
to your incredible power!
Please, sir!
Can you tell the folks
at home a little bit
about who you are
and why you came to our city?!
[GOHAN]
Hm! You bet! Sure!
[NICK HORNBY]
Mm! Huh?
[GOHAN]
Hiyaaa! Ho! Here we go!
I'm the man with the plan!
To uplift the good!
And root out the bad!
'Til we're living
like we should!
Hiyaaa! Whoa, ho!
Uh, huh!
Now you understand that
I'm the... Great Saiyaman!
Blah! What a geek!
[BULMA] So I heard you're
going to take part
in the World Martial
Arts Championship!
Yeah.
Wow! Well I must say,
I'm a little surprised, Gohan!
It's not like you have to
prove yourself or anything!
[GOHAN] I know! But Videl
Satan discovered my secret!
She's blackmailing me into it!
Again?! Good grief, Gohan!
You get blackmailed
more than a politician!
What is it with you
and all these girls!
"Videl Satan"...
That sounds so familiar!
[BULMA gasps] She's not that
goon Mr. Satan's daughter?
That's her!
She's a classmate of mine
at Orange Star High School!
She's nice! Always
fighting crime like I am!
She's a good girl!
But I've never met
anyone as obstinate
and pushy as she is.
Except for my mom.
And now that she
knows who I am,
she's determined to show
that she's stronger than me
by beating me
in the tournament!
[TRUNKS thinking] Man!
Gohan's such a nerd sometimes!
If it was me, I'd just
beat that ol' girl up!
[BULMA] So this Videl girl
is rude and pushy, huh?!
Just to you, or to everyone!
[GOHAN]
Just to me!
I see!
[GOHAN] Ever since
I showed up as Saiyaman
she's been hounding me
and saying that
she wouldn't rest
until she unmasked me!
And she's not the type of girl
that you can keep a secret from!
Gohan, it sounds to me like
this girl likes you, silly!
I know it sounds strange,
but that's the way
girls operate sometimes!
There's a good chance
that you could get out of
competing in the tournament
by asking her out on a date!
Nope! Tried that!
She wasn't interested!
Not her! I think what she
really wants is to beat me up!
I'm afraid I'm gonna
have to compete!
But they don't allow
head protection
in the tournament, so I need to
come up with a new disguise!
Ahhh! What a shame!
You don't see superheros
wearing helmets very often!
It's a nice touch!
[TRUNKS]
Actually it's kinda stupid!
[GOHAN]
Videl did call it a trash can...
Ouchee! That hurts!
I guess I don't know
what's "in" nowadays!
I must be getting old!
Let's see!
We need to come up with
something simple, yet chic!
And I think I know
just the thing!
[BULMA] Taaa-daaa!
Well, whatd'ya guys think?!
All right! I love it!
Now that's what I call style!
Hey! Whatd'ya think, Trunks?!
Pretty cool, huh?!
Yeah, it's great!
[TRUNKS thinking]
If you like looking like
a total geek that is!
I think you look very cool!
But make sure you like it
because your
picture's gonna be
plastered everywhere
after you win!
[VEGETA]
Who says he's going to win?!
[GOHAN, BULMA]
Huh?
[BULMA]
Who could possibly beat him?!
Yours truly, that's who!
If you'll enter, I'll enter!
[GOHAN gasps]
[VEGETA] You were a lot stronger
than me when we fought Cell.
But while you've been
hanging out in the library
and going out on dates,
I've been doing nothing but
severe training
the entire time!
Yep! That's all
you've been doing,
I can vouch for that!
How come you Saiyans
can train all day long
but you can't mow the lawn
or take out the trash!
[GOHAN]
Uh...
This is cool! Dad and Gohan
are gonna fight! Wow!
[GOKU]
I think I'll enter, too!
[ALL]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Gohan!
[GOHAN gasps] Is that you, Dad?!
Please tell me that it's you!
No way! Wow!
[VEGETA]
Hm? Kakarot?
[GOHAN] It's you! Dad!
It's really you!
Hi, Son! It's great to
hear your voice again!
Dad! Unbelievable!
You're here!
Where is he?
Trunks, you haven't been
telling Gohan the truth
about his costume, have you?!
[KING KAI laughs]
This is great! Father!
Are you really coming back
to compete in the
World Championships?!
Yeah! I'm allowed to
come back for one day!
Baba checked it out for me!
It appears I have
a little credit!
I'm excited! I can't
wait to see everyone!
Tell your mom
that I'm coming back!
For a whole day!
[GOKU laughs]
All right! Yes!
He's flipped, Dad!
No, son! His dad's coming back!
Even I'm excited, Kakarot!
At having another
chance to defeat you!
[GOKU]
Mm-hm! We'll see!
I guess anything's possible!
Miracles do happen!
Miracles, huh?!
Oh, I can't wait!
[GOHAN laughs]
This is great! Gohan!
After you tell your mom,
you should go to Master Roshi's!
Krillin's gonna flip
when he hears!
Right! Definitely!
[TRUNKS]
Who's he?
[GOHAN]
An old friend, Trunks! Oh, hey!
Vegeta, if you're
gonna compete,
you should wear a disguise!
Maybe something like mine!
[VEGETA]
Rrrgh! No way!
I wouldn't be
caught dead in that thing!
[GOHAN]
See you later, guys!
I'm gonna swing by
Master Roshi's
and then tell Mom
and Goten the news!
Tell everyone I said hi!
See ya!
Aw... There he goes!
I hope he comes back soon!
Man! Mom's gonna freak out!
This is so awesome!
[GOHAN laughs]
Yeah! Woo-hoo! Yeah!
[GOHAN thinking]
My Dad! He's always been
so full of surprises!
[FARMER humming]
[GOHAN]
Woo-hoooo!
[FARMER yelps]
I'll be darned!
[GIRL panting]
[BOAR MAN cackles]
Enough of this! Take her out!
[BOAR MAN growls, grunts]
[GIRL screams]
[BOAR MAN grunts]
[GOHAN]
Hmm!
[GOHAN yells]
[BOARMAN yelps]
[KHAKI MAN, BOARMAN groan]
Shame on you!
Shooting a gun
at a helpless lady!
Fool! Idiot! Dope!
[GOHAN laughs] All wrong!
Not even close, friend!
Yaaah! So you wanna
know my name, huh?!
I am the defender
of justice! And truth!
I... am... the Great--
[GIRL grunts]
[GIRL]
You big dummy! How dare you!
What do you think you're doing?!
Now I have to
do it all over again!
It took me all day
to get that take right
and when I finally did,
you blew it!
[DIRECTOR] Cut! What the heck
is going on down there?!
Saiyaman's not supposed
to be in this scene!
Hey! You! That was
a great stunt,
but we've got to stick
to the script! Understand?!
[GOHAN]
Who me?! Me, sir?!
No, my mom!
Of course you! Hot Shot!
There are plenty
of stuntmen in this town!
The next time you
do that you're fired!
I am?
Places! Let's see if we can
get it right this time, people!
[CREW]
Aw, man!
[BOARMAN]
We almost had it, dude!
[KHAKI MAN]
Yeah! That guy was crazy!
He's lucky we didn't kill him!
They're... actors?
All right! Let's get
it right now, folks!
We're almost a week behind
schedule as it is!
[GOHAN]
Wow! I can't believe it!
They're actually making
a movie out of Saiyaman!
Goten's gonna flip!
[DIRECTOR]
Camera!
[CAMERA MAN]
Rolling!
[DIRECTOR]
Action!
[SAIYAMAN]
No! I'm scared of heights!
Please! Don't let go!
Nobody told me that
I'd have to do this!
Don't let go! Please!
Whatever you do, don't let go!
Let me off this thing!
Excuse me, sir!
What are we gonna do?!
We're going to fire him,
that's what!
I can't believe this,
that guy was a
dead ringer for Saiyaman!
Where are we going to find
another guy like that?!
We're already a week behind!
[GOHAN laughs] Do you really
think that guy looks like me?!
What?! You?!
[GOHAN] Well, I just
mean like Saiyaman!
I think I look alot more
like Saiyaman than he does!
He doesn't look
anything like Saiyaman!
Darn it! You're right!
But at this point,
I'll take anybody!
Even a pathetic guy like that!
[DIRECTOR] All right, people!
Places! This is it!
Uhh! Excuse me, sir!
What exactly am I
supposed to do?!
[DIRECTOR] Announce to
the villains who you are!
Now! Are you ready?!
[GOHAN]
Yeah!
[DIRECTOR] All right, Hot Shot,
let's see what you've got!
Camera?!
[ASST. DIRECTOR]
Saiyaman Arrives! Take one!
--[CAMERA MAN] Rolling.
--[DIRECTOR] Action!
I am the defender
of liberty and justice!
Champion of the weak!
Shielder of oppression!
Cut!
Uh?
What the heck was that?!
No! No! No! No! Look!
You're a superhero, you fool!
Why are you dancing
around like a cheerleader?!
Hm?! Cheerleader?!
Now do it like Saiyaman!
Take note! Peace will
prevail on Earth!
Saiyaman is here!
Preposterous!
Love is the answer! Not war!
[DIRECTOR]
Cut!
I have come to set
the captives free!
Evil will shudder
when it hears my name!
[DIRECTOR]
No!
Downpressors will
have nowhere to hide!
[DIRECTOR]
No, no, no!
I am the Great Saiyaman!
Cut! Enough! Enough!
Knock it off!
We're not trying
to spoof Saiyaman
and make him look like an idiot!
This is a serious
action-adventure movie!
But... I... was serious!
Nonsense! I know your type!
Punks! Shape up, kid!
Now! Or your career's over!
Right! Sir!
[ASST. DIRECTOR]
All right everybody! Places!
This is the
Saiyaman Jump scene!
Huh?! Oh, man!
Look how late it is!
I need to tell Mom the news!
And I still have to
make it to Master Roshi's.
Quiet! Now! Ready?! Action!
[DIRECTOR]
Just jump, bonehead!
Stick your arms out and fly!
It's not dangerous!
That's a professional
crane operator over there!
Hey!
[DIRECTOR] Now stop
being a coward and jump!
I'm afraid I have to go!
Yes! Yes!
Are you getting this!
Yes! Yes! Oh! No!
[CREW yells]
Sorry! Gotta get going! Bye!
It's not possible!
Tell me it's not true!
He was the real thing!
[KRILLIN] What?! No way!
Goku's gonna compete!
I don't believe it!
This is amazing! Wow!
Hey guys... This is Krillin.
He doesn't fight anymore
so he let his hair grow out.
Goku! Well, whaddya know...?
[KRILLIN] Well if you and Goku
and Vegeta are going to enter,
why should I enter?!
[GOHAN] Aw, c'mon, Krillin!
It'll be great!
[KRILLIN]
I know it would be fun and all!
It would be like
old times again!
Fighting in another
World Championship with Goku
almost sounds
too good to be true!
But I have to
start training a lot
and I don't know how
my wife would feel about that!
--[GOHAN] Hm?
--[KRILLIN] Huh?
[MARON] Hey, Dad!
Get the ball! Get it, Dad!
[KRILLIN] There you go,
Maron, you little fire-fly!
That a girl!
Wow! She's adorable, Krillin!
How would you
like to see your Dad
compete in a
Martial Arts tournament?!
[EIGHTEEN]
First she'd wanna know
if there's any
prize money involved!
[GOHAN]
Oh, hi! Nice to see ya!
And yeah, they pay out
to the top five places!
First, the overall winner
of the tournament
gets paid ten million Zeni!
Then it goes on down!
Second place gets paid
five million...
and third place
gets three million...
Enter, Krillin! I will! Why not?
[KRILLIN]
Hmm...
[MARON]
Hey, dad!
If you fight, I'll watch you!
[KRILLIN]
Thanks, sweetheart!
[EIGHTEEN]
Come on, Krillin!
[MARON]
Yeah! Come on, Dad!
You'll win if you do!
If you say so! I'll do it!
Hey! Maybe I
should enter, too!
Whatd'ya think?!
[MARON]
No way! You're too old!
Hey, Gohan, let's not
tell Piccolo about it,
that way, I'll have
a better chance
of getting into the top-five!
Oh! I don't know, Krillin!
I was gonna tell him, too!
All right! But if you
won't do me this favor,
I'm gonna have to be
honest about your outfit!
[GOHAN]
Huh?! What do you mean?!
I'm at the pinnacle of style!
I think you've
lost your fashion sense
living way out here so long!
Ciao! See ya at
the tournament!
Goku? If he's entering,
it should be one to remember!
[GOHAN]
So, whatd'ya say?!
[PICCOLO] Sure, kid, I'll do it!
It actually sounds like fun!
[POPO] I'll bet Dende would
enjoy the tournament as well!
That sounds great! Yeah! Come!
Hey, thanks! But, I'm not
much of a fighter, Gohan!
I think I'd better
stick to healing!
[PICCOLO]
I do have one question!
You're not going to wear that
in the tournament, are you?
What?! Man! Not you, too!
You don't think
my outfit looks good?!
[PICCOLO] Mmm. Gohan... I can't
lie to you. It's ridiculous!
Oh, my!
Of all people! Piccolo!
I can't believe it! Really!
He wears a turban
for goodness sake
and those pointy,
little booties!
And who knows what that is that
he drapes over his shoulders!
Oh my gosh!
Come to think of it,
I used to dress just like him
all those years
when I was a kid!
Man! Now I know why he said
my outfit looks ridiculous--
he's jealous!
You know! I guess I haven't
even asked my mom
if I can participate
in the World Championships!
[GOHAN] Wouldn't that be great:
Gohan, son of Goku,
will not be taking part in the
World Championships this year
because his mommy won't let him!
How can it be possible that
a guy who saved the world
still has to take orders
from his mother?!
Whaaat! My gosh!
Goku's coming back
after all this time!
This is unbelievable!
[GOHAN]
Mm-hm.
[CHICHI] Oh, my goodness!
I hardly know what to think!
Your father's
really coming home!
Good news, son! You get
to meet your daddy!
Isn't that wonderful?!
You get to meet
your daddy! Ohhh!
Good heavens, boys!
This is too good to be true!
I'm in trouble
though, aren't I?!
I look so old now
and Goku probably
hasn't aged a bit!
People don't age in
Other World, do they?!
Maybe if I have a facial
and get my hair done
and I keep myself
from crying so my face
doesn't get all puffy!
Whatd'ya think boys?
[GOHAN]
Yeah, sure, Mom!
And, uh,  by the way,
since Dad's competing in
the World Championships, you
think I could compete as well?
Mmmm! Wow! My stars! Huh?
Gohan, what are you saying?!
[GOHAN]
That I'd like your permission
to enter the
World Championships
and to miss some school
so I can train...
What?! Are you serious?!
[GOHAN]
Yeah, of course!
[CHICHI] Ahhhh! Gohan,
you've got to be kidding!
You know your studies take
priority over everything else!
What's wrong with you?!
[GOHAN] Mom! Dad's only
gonna be here for a day!
And I'll never get
this chance again!
[CHICHI] You'll never
get this chance to prepare
for college again
if you blow this one, Gohan!
[GOHAN] But the winner gets
paid ten million Zeni, Mom!
If I win, it will be like
getting a big scholarship!
[CHICHI shrieks] You could get
a PHD with that kind of cash!
Wow! My son, a PHD!
How wonderful!
Of course, you can compete
in the tournament, Gohan!
Of course you can!
[GOHAN]
Goodnight, Goten!
[GOTEN]
Goodnight, Gohan!
Hey! You're gonna help
me train, aren't you?
I'm going to need a
real strong training partner!
Sure!
[GOTEN]
Gohan?
[GOHAN]
Hmm?
[GOTEN]
What's my dad like?!
[GOHAN]
He's like an angel, Goten!
[GOTEN]
What's an angel, like?
[GOHAN]
I don't know!
I just know that
when they're around,
you feel happy inside!
All right! Nice warm-up!
Now! Let's get started!
[GOHAN] This is a little
trick Dad taught me!
Pretty cool,
wouldn't ya say?
Yeah!
[GOHAN chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
Gohan has begun his training
for the World
Martial Arts Championship!
And with Goku joining in,
and all of the
Z-fighters following suit,
this tournament promises
to be the best one ever!