[NARRATOR] Last time
on DragonBall Z,
Trunks and Cell pushed their
powers to incredible new levels.
And you'll be the first to see
the true power
of the Saiyan race!
[TRUNKS yells]
[NARRATOR] Trunks beefed up
his body and ascended to a
level never before
seen on planet Earth.
As his muscles bulged and raw
power pumped through his veins,
the sinister android
watched silently.
Trunks may have become
stronger than Vegeta,
but he hasn't won yet.
[TRUNKS yells]
[NARRATOR] The biggest
challenge of Trunks' life
stands before him.
And the Saiyan from the future
shows no signs of backing down.
[NARRATOR] After a slew
of well-delivered punches,
Trunks proved that he
was a force not to be ignored.
With fierce determination, he
hammered Cell into the ground.
[NARRATOR] But still,
Cell laughed.
[CELL chuckles]
Impressive, I must admit
you have exceeded me, Trunks.
At least in the area
of brute strength.
And yet you have absolutely
no chance of defeating me!
[TRUNKS] Listen to yourself!
What kind of logic is that?!
Oh, you'll see...
[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR] What could he mean?
Find out today!
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL chuckles]
[ANDROID 16 thinking] Where does
he get his strength from?
[TRUNKS yells]
[yelling continues]
Not bad, Trunks. But give up.
You just can't beat me.
[TRUNKS growls]
[VEGETA grunts]
What's wrong!?
Vegeta, are you okay?
[VEGETA grunts]
[KRILLIN] Hang in there.
I gotta find a safe place
to set you down.
That island over there
will have to do!
[KRILLIN] Vegeta,
can you hear me?
Hey, come on... wake up...
Take this. It's a Senzu bean.
Hey, Vegeta! You okay?
[VEGETA] Cell!
[VEGETA growls]
[TRUNKS growls]
[growling continues]
[CELL chuckles]
Trunks... He's so powerful.
He's even stronger than
Cell now. It's incredible!
[BULMA] Hey, guys?
What's going on?
A little play-by-play for
those of us in the cheap seats
would really be
appreciated, you know?
Trunks is big
and strong, alright?!
Trunks? Oh, of course!
I'm so proud of my little boy!
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS yells]
[CELL chuckles]
[GOKU] Okay, Gohan! When you're
ready, show me what you can do!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN thinking] I've got
to focus my emotions better!
This has to get easier!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOKU] Hmm...?
Whoa... He's really starting
to get the hang of it.
That's my boy! He's going
to be a great warrior someday.
[GOHAN thinking]
What is my Dad doing?
He's been just sitting there
watching me for days.
I guess he's trying to
figure out how to ascend
to the next level.
It must be really tough.
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN sighs]
[GOKU] Gohan, watch me.
[GOKU yells]
[yelling continues]
[GOHAN gasps]
He did it!
[GOHAN] Dad! You did it!
Your power...
It's huge! You did it!
You ascended to the next level.
I could go one step
further if I wanted to.
[GOKU yells]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Yeah, that's it!
Wow! You're more than a Super
Saiyan now! You're the greatest!
Nobody can beat you!
I know you can beat Cell!
[GOKU thinking] No, this
new form has a weakness.
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL]
You're too slow, Trunks.
You'll have to do
better than that.
Cell! Darn him! I can't
hit him. Why can't I hit him?!
[CELL] What a
disappointment you are!
You're so pathetic, I can't even
test my complete power on you.
What?!
[TRUNKS yells]
[CELL chuckles]
[TRUNK grunts]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[blows landing,
TRUNKS grunting]
[CELL] Are you finished yet?
Or are you going to get up
and entertain me some more?
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Get up or I will
put you down permanently!
[CELL chuckles]
That's it!
[TRUNKS growls]
You're wasting your strength!
[TRUNKS grunts]
I told you before,
you can't beat me.
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS snarls]
[TRUNKS thinking] I can't even
hit him! I don't understand!
I've powered up so much.
Why can't I touch him?
[GOHAN] You can beat Cell!
You can! I know you can!
Not in this form, not yet.
What? Why not, Dad?
[GOKU] I know I look
like I can, Gohan.
But these bulky muscles
make it hard to move fast.
And if I'm going to beat Cell,
I can't have anything
slowing me down.
I may have great power,
but what good is it
if I can't catch my enemy?
It takes more than brute
strength to win a fight.
And transformations
waste a lot of energy.
You've been finding
that out yourself
when you've turned into a Super
Saiyan. It's not easy, right?
Right?!
Right.
[GOKU] We can't afford
to waste all that energy.
But at the same time, we need
the Super Saiyan power! You see?
Somehow, we have to
get to a point where it
feels natural to
be a Super Saiyan,
so that we can stay
like that all the time!
I want you try being a Super
Saiyan for the whole day.
We'll slow down our training
until it stops...
feeling so weird...
Yeah! Dad... I'll
do the best I can!
Amateur.
[CELL chuckles
You said you'd show
me true Saiyan power.
But all that you've done is
pump up your little muscles.
And there's nothing
special about that.
I could do that too,
if I wanted.
[CELL grunts]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL growls]
[CELL] You see?
It's rather easy to transform
and flaunt your powers.
But it's not going to get you
anywhere if your opponent
has any sort of speed!
You fool.
Honestly, it's a very simple
concept to understand.
Even Vegeta figured it out.
So, why can't you?
Oh, of course! That's why father
stopped getting stronger...
He... He could have, but
he knew about its limits!
[TRUNKS] And I just kept plowing
forward. Like a stupid child...
You can finish me
if you want. I've failed.
How very gracious of you.
Hey! How come Trunks' energy
suddenly decreased so fast?
It... doesn't make
sense... What happened?!
Cell... He's still
just as strong!
And now I can't
feel Trunks at all...
Oh no... maybe Cell beat him!
[VEGETA] Fine by me,
I'll take him!
[KRILLIN] Hey! Wait a minute!
I wait for no one!
Now Cell is mine!
But, you're hurt!
[VEGETA] Leave me alone.
[KRILLIN sighs]
What was I thinking?
I mean, it's just no use trying
to talk any sense into Vegeta.
Here we go again...
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
[TIEN whimpers]
[PICCOLO growls]
What's up? Hasn't Trunks
put Cell's lights out yet?
It's over!
He did it? Trunks beat him?
No... he means Cell
has beaten Trunks.
[BULMA gasps]
This is bad... very bad!
What?! That means he's
in danger! Do something!
[CELL] What shall I do with you?
[CELL] Such an
interesting predicament.
Both you and Vegeta
have disappointed me.
I expected more of a challenge
from a pair of Super Saiyans.
However, there is something
that I am curious about.
I see you're very strong.
How did you become so powerful?
It's hard to believe
that you could develop
those fighting skills
in such a short time.
Tell me... how did you do it?
What is the secret
of your power?
[CELL] Don't want to talk?
Well, let me ask you this...
If you had more time,
could you get stronger?
[TRUNKS] Huh?!
Could you?
Maybe! What difference
does it make now?!
And why would you
even want to know?
[CELL chuckles]
Oh, just curious that's all.
One more question:
Where has Goku been?
And where has he been hiding?
For your information,
he's training to defeat you.
And make no mistake Cell, he
will be the one who beats you!
He'll take you, no contest!
No contest? Then, a tournament!
What do you mean?
[PICCOLO] What? No!
I don't believe it!
[BULMA] What happened?
Is Trunks alright?
Yeah, for now! Cell is planning
some kind of tournament!
[ALL gasp]
A tournament...?
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] The tournament
will begin in 10 days...
And onsider yourself lucky that
I am giving you a second chance.
But, what are you talking about?
You really don't know, do you?
Long before we ever existed,
there was a competition
on this planet called the
"World Martial Arts Tournament."
I'm going to revive it
and prove once and for all
that I have no equal.
Each member of your
team may challenge me.
I will fight them one-on-one,
and when I win...
I'll face the next
challenger on your team.
Do you understand? Bring me
all the opponents you can.
The more fighters you bring...
the more chances
you'll have to survive!
[CELL] I have yet to decide a
location of the tournament,
so keep an eye on your
television for details.
[TRUNKS] The television?
It should be very entertaining.
[CELL chuckles]
Alright. Oh, and make
sure you bring plenty
of those Senzu beans.
Wait, tell me! What is the
real purpose of this tournament?
What are you
really going to do?!
Cell... I know what
you Androids are like!
I'm sure this is some
sort of a trick.
Just a trap to get us
all in one place, right?!
[CELL] Oh, must you
always treat everything
like it's the
end of the world?
There is no secret purpose.
I simply want to get as much
out of this planet as I can,
before I destroy it!
I have proven that
I am unstoppable.
Neither you or your friends
are any threat to me now.
However, there is one
that I want to test
my complete power against...
I want you to bring me Goku.
This tournament is sure
to be a guaranteed hit!
Everyone will be watching
me... I just can't wait
to see that look
of panic and fear!
[TRUNKS gasps]
That's it! That's the look!
[CELL laughs]
Until then...
[NARRATOR] Who
would have imagined
such a shocking turn of events?
By reviving the world
martial arts tournament,
Cell plans to
humiliate his opponents
in front of a live
television audience!
Talk about adding
insult to injury.
[NARRATOR] In only ten short
days, the tournament will begin.
The prize for the winner?
Control of the world!
Our heroes had better train hard
because it's time to put their
Super Saiyan
abilities to the test
next time on Dragon Ball Z!