[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
an old foe from
Goku's past resurfaced
and was terrorizing some
of the local villagers.
[GENERAL TAO] Fire!
[LIME] Ahhh!
[NARRATOR] Little did
he know, a special guest
was among the
villagers that day.
[GENERAL TAO] Say what?!
What happened?!
I happened! That's what!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
Piccolo was a little short
on training partners,
so he used his patented
Split Form Technique
to get the ball rolling!
[PICCOLO B growls]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[NARRATOR] It was Piccolo versus
Piccolo, Namek versus Namek,
in a raging battle that would
end up in a stalemate.
[LAO] Beat Cell!
I know you can do it!
[BOTH] Huh?
I know you'll
both be there!
At the big tournament, right?
[LIME] Goodbye, Gohan!
Come back and see us soon!
[NARRATOR] And so,
with only eight days left
until the start
of the tournament,
our heroes headed home
with thoughts of good food,
relaxing in the sunshine,
and of enjoying every moment
they had left
together to the fullest.
[KRILLIN] So Vegeta's furious
and he's about to kill him
for cutting off his tail, and
Yajirobe goes, "Please, sir!
I really admire you and
I'd like to join you
if it's not too late!"
--[KRILLIN laughs]
--[GOKU &amp; GOHAN laugh]
[BOTH] Huh?!
Man, again?
You gotta control it!
Like this! Watch me. See?
Huh?!
[CHICHI] I don't believe it!
Not another one!
--Goku! This has got to stop!
--[GOKU] Sorry! Oh, no!
[GOHAN] Dad, your chair! Whoa!
--[GOKU] Gohan, here! Ooops!
--[KRILLIN] Goku! Yikes!
--Guys! Lookout!
--Oh, man!
[GOKU &amp; GOHAN sighs]
[GOKU] Oh man, we really
did it this time!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN] ChiChi's
gonna kill you guys!
Hey! Where'd she go?!
[CHICHI screams]
Here I am!
Alright, you two!
I've had it with this
Super Saiyan stuff!
You've broken both sets of
dishes and three tables!
I swear!
Is it too much to ask
to have a normal dinner
where we don't smash
glasses and bend silverware
and break all the furniture?!
Well?! Is it?! I'm waiting!
No, sorry...
I have an idea.
Maybe we should use
paper plates and cups.
Yeah?! Well,
think again, kid!
Gosh! What a funny
sense of humor!
Paper cups and paper plates!
You must get that
from your mommy!
I'll tell you what, Gohan.
Since it's your birthday,
I'm going to let you off easy.
For your punishment,
you can help me clean up.
As for you, Goku,
hit the road!
Don't call us! We'll call you!
Uh, you want me
to leave home?
[CHICHI] Yes! I can't
take it anymore, Goku!
I need you gone!
At least until I finish setting
up for Gohan's party!
You like to fish, right?!
So go catch a fish or something!
Hey, sure! That sounds great!
I'll catch a big one!
I'll go too!
Me too!
[CHICHI] Wonderful plan,
but you can forget it, Gohan!
[ALL] Huh?
Look! If you think you're
getting off the hook that easy,
you can think
again, kiddo!
After you finish cleaning up,
it's time to study!
Anything but that, Mom!
A mother knows
what's best, right?!
Well, I guess...
[GOKU] Hey, Gohan.
Your mother's a
hundred percent right.
It would be best if you
studied this afternoon.
[GOHAN gasps]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[CHICHI screams]
--[ALL groan]
--[GOKU] Huh?
What'd I do?!
You don't know?
Gosh, Daddy!
Are you sick?!
[GOKU grunts]
You feel okay...
[GOKU] Ionno?
[CHICHI hums]
Ahh!
I always feel like humming a
tune when Gohan is studying.
I hope Goku feels
more like himself
after he fishes
for a while.
I think this whole Cell thing
is beggining to get to him
a little bit...
One thing's for sure though.
I wouldn't want
to be a fish right now.
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Whoo-hoo! Alright!
Yeah-ha!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU yells heartily]
[GOKU] I gotcha!
[GOKU laughs]
[KRILLIN laughs]
Man, I tell ya! Some things
just never change!
[GOKU growling]
I ate your friend!
Now it's your turn!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[GOKU laughs]
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GOKU laughs]
[KRILLIN laughs]
You know, I don't get it, Goku.
I mean, Gohan's at home studying
and we're out
having fun fishing!
You must be pretty darn sure
we're going to beat Cell
if we're not gonna do anything
to prepare for the tournament.
[GOKU grunts]
Not at all.
Huh?!
[GOKU] To tell you the truth,
I'm not sure if we have
what it takes to beat Cell.
I have no idea.
Only time will tell. But I
don't want Gohan and Chichi
to worry, I want them
to enjoy themselves.
These are precious
times, Krillin...
Being together is everything.
That's all that really
matters to me right now...
[thinking] Yeah...
[CHICHI] Now what happened
to that tablecloth?
I could have sworn that I put it
under here with all this junk.
Ow!
Oh, wow! The old family album!
Ahh!
Oh my gosh! The wedding!
Typical Goku...
[CHICHI gasps]
[CHICHI] My goodness!
I can't believe it!
It seems like yesterday!
He's so cute...
[GOHAN snores softly]
Gosh, look how tiny he is.
Of course! He's a baby, silly.
Uhh... Don't you think it's
time you give the boy a name?
I've thought of one.
It came to me last night.
Oh... I didn't know
you picked already...
Yes. "Einstein!"
[BOTH] Hmm? Einstein?!
You're kidding!
Hardly! Our boy's name
is going to be Einstein!
[GOHAN cries]
Huh?
[crying continues]
Aww There, there, boy.
I don't think he likes the name
you picked out for him, hun!
Nonsense, Dad!
Look! He's fine about
the name Einstein!
[GOHAN cries]
He hates the name, honey!
[CHICHI] Well, what do you think
we should call him, Dad?
[OX-KING] Oh, I don't know!
Uhhh... I did scribble
a few names down...
Ahh... There!
Here we are!
[CHICHI &amp; GOKU] Uhh.
[OX-KING] Hm! Let's see here!
Ox-King Jr, Ox-Monkey!
Big Ox! Oxford!
Oh, you'll like these!
Ox in the Box! Ox-man!
Johnny Ox-seed!
[GOHAN wails]
Huh?
Well! He hates them too!
I'll be darned!
[clock ticking]
[GOHAN babbles]
[BOTH sigh]
[GOKU] Guys, I think
I'm gonna go fishing.
[BOTH] No way!
[GOKU] Hm? Why?
Because we have a
nameless boy, that's why!
Goku! At least
think of one!
One?
[BOTH] Hmmm...
One!
[BOTH] Mm-hmm!
Well, sure! But
can we eat first?
I'm starving!
[BOTH sigh]
You're hungry, huh?!
How can you think of food
when your son's lying
there without a name?!
Uhh...
[CHICHI] I know you were
raised in the woods,
but surely Gohan taught
you some manners?!
--[GOHAN giggles]
--[OX-KING] Huh?
Goku! Answer me, please!
Were you taught anything that
resembles manners by Gohan?
--[GOHAN babbles]
--Not really... Uh-uh.
[OX-KING gasps]
[CHICHI] You just use the
fact that you were raised
in the woods as an excuse
for being totally uncouth!
[OX-KING] I think you
found it, ChiChi!
--[CHICHI] Found what?!
--[OX-KING] The name!
Watch this, honey!
Gohan!
--[GOHAN giggles]
--[OX-KING] See! He likes it!
Gohan!
[GOHAN giggles]
[BOTH gasp]
[OX-KING] Gohan!
--[GOHAN giggles]
--[CHICHI] Oh, my goodness, Dad!
I think you're right!
[GOKU] The four-star ball...
Grandpa's ball!
--[GOHAN laughs]
--How cool!
He really wants to have
old grandpa's name!
Wow!
I know Gohan would be so proud
if you named your son
after him, wherever he is!
I guess I can wait
for the next one!
Well! Hear that, Gohan?
That's your name!
--[GOHAN laughs]
--[CHICHI sighs]
Gohan! Is that what
you want to be called?
Yeah! Gohan!
--[GOHAN laughs]
--Yeah! G-G-G-Gohan!
[GOKU &amp; GOHAN laugh]
Oh, Goku...
[CHICHI growls]
[GOHAN] Hm...
--[CHICHI] Gohan!
--[GOHAN] Mom!
I'm really studying
this time! I swear!
Don't swear! You know
better than that, right?!
Yes...
Now clean up this mess so you
can go out fish with your dad!
Sure!
[DIRECTOR] Get down!
[REPORTER grunts]
[REPORTER] Alright, folks!
You got a glimpse.
And now, at great risk,
we're going in
for a better look!
[REPORTER] Standing at a
distance before you,
in a stadium that he made
himself, is the monster, Cell,
who has challenged
the entire planet
to match his strength and skill
in a Martial Arts Tournament.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if I don't make it through this,
remember me, if you will,
for what I'm doing here today.
[REPORTER] That's him folks!
The one who calls himself Cell!
Who has brought the
world to a standstill
with his deadly challenge.
Oh, gosh! I just can't do
this! Can we go home?!
I've lost my nerve!
Find it!
[REPORTER] Awe, gee...
[REPORTER] Excuse me, Cell!
I'm from KBC News.
And I was, uh, hoping
if you could tell us
where you came from
and why you've chosen the Earth
as the host planet for
your Cell Games?
And of course, if you're
too busy to answer
I completely and totally
understand, Mister Cell!
Uuh?
Here's my answer.
[REPORTER gasps]
[CAMERAMAN &amp; DIRECTOR scream]
[DIRECTOR] Wait,
the show must go on!
[CAMERA MAN] Forget you!
[REPORTER whimpers]
[CELL] Now. Say your prayers.
[screaming]
[KRILLIN] Man!
Check those babies out!
[GOKU] I know!
This old tree always
has the best apples!
Gosh! They're huge!
[GOKU] Mm-hm!
Nothing but the best!
I hope you don't mind
one more round, old fella!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] There! That
should do the trick!
And it didn't hurt
a bit, did it, old timer?
[KRILLIN gasps]
[low rumbling]
[GOKU] Here they come!
Wow! Get ready, you guys!
Huh?
Hey, wait! Oh, I'ma get this--
Ha-- I got it-- This o-- Wait!
Oh that one must've-- Oh.
I got it-- Hey! Here!
I miss it! Oh, this one-- Oh!
I got this one!
Huh?!
Hey!
Looking for these?
Wow! Awesome! Pretty cool! Man!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOKU] Ahh... I guess
we'd better head back.
[KRILLIN] Oh, hey, look!
We missed one!
It's in the hole in the tree.
Huh?
[thinking] Gosh!
It's been so many years...
[CHICHI] Ahh! This
has always been
my favorite part of the woods!
[GOKU] I think
Gohan likes it, too!
[GOHAN babbles,
CHICHI giggles]
[CHICHI] I guess so!
[GOKU] Everything's so lush
out here in the spring.
[CHICHI] Mmm!
[CHICHI gasps]
Oh, wow! Look!
[CHICHI giggles]
They're beautiful!
And what a smell!
It's heavenly, Goku, isn't it?!
[GOKU] It sure is!
[CHICHI] Oh, hey guys,
look! Up there! In the tree!
A mommy and a daddy and a baby!
Just like in our family!
Aw, how cute!
[GOKU sighs]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Hey! What d'ya think, Gohan?!
Hmm?
[BOTH scream]
[CHICHI] Goku!
There goes our son!
[GOHAN screams]
[CHICHI] Goku, do something!
[screaming continues]
[CHICHI &amp; GOKU] Gohan!
[GOHAN screams]
[CHICHI screams]
[GOKU] Oh, no! He's
heading for that ravine!
[GOHAN screams]
[CHICHI] Gohan!
[GOKU]
[CHICHI] Goku, he's going
to smash into that tree!
You've got to stop him!
[GOHAN wails]
[CHICHI shrieks]
[GOKU yells]
Nooo!
[GOHAN screams]
[GOKU] Gohan!
[GOHAN screaming]
[BOTH screaming]]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOHAN sighs]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU sighs]
[CHICHI] Gohan!
Ohh! Is he alright?!
Oh, my goodness!
Gohan!
Hm?
What's wrong with him?
He's not even scared!
He's totally fine!
[CHICHI sighs]
[CHICHI] That was awful!
And you just think it was a big
amusement park ride, don't you?
Well, you're lucky
your dad saved you!
Uhh, not me!
Your daddy's not taking
any credit, is he?
Of course, since this whole
thing is your fault,
you shouldn't!
You should never taken your
hand off that baby carriage!
You can be so
irresponsible, Goku!
Yep! You're right!
[CHICHI] Why is it so hard
to stay mad at you?
Your dad's too much,
isn't he, Gohan?
I swear! Bye, Goku!
[GOKU] Hey, ChiChi! U-Uhh...
Hmmm... Huh?
[GOKU] Man! I've never
seen anything like it!
It's a miracle!
[GOHAN] Hello in there!
Earth to Daddy!
[GOKU] Oops! Sorry!
[KRILLIN] I'm not
even going to ask.
I don't even want to know
what goes on inside
that head of yours.
[GOKU] Hey! What do
you mean by that?!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laugh]
[ALL laughing]
[OX-KING] My grandson's
growing up!
[CHICHI] He sure is!
[KRILLIN] Wow!
Look at that cake!
It has all your faces on it!
That's really
incredible, ChiChi!
Yeah, thanks, Mom!
I think you're really going
to like what I got you, Gohan!
Look!
Wow! Thanks, Grandpa!
Do you think I could I open
my presents now, Mom?
No! Not yet! Cake first! Time
to blow out the candles!
Cake! Yum!
Make sure that you
make a wish first!
[GOHAN] Okay,
I think I've got one!
[GOHAN thinking] I wish for
the strength to beat Cell,
so my family can live in peace.
--[OX-KING &amp; KRILLIN gasp]
--[GOKU] Look out!
[CHICHI] Oh, no!
[KRILLIN] Holy cow!
[GOHAN gasps]
[OX-KING] ChiChi!
Are you alright, honey?!
[CHICHI] I have icing
in my nose, Dad!
--What do you think?!
--[GINYU] Ribbit! Ribbit!
[GOKU] Mmm! Gosh!
This is delicious!
--Where's your piece, Gohan?
--[GOHAN chuckles]
[KRILLIN] If I'm not mistaken,
I think it went down my shirt.
[chuckling continues]
[OX-KING] Ahh! A strawberry!
Gohan!
I know, Mom...
I'm in trouble...
[CHICHI]
You're darn right you are!
A normal kid would be
severely punished for trashing
his entire birthday cake
on his birthday!
--[CHICHI giggles]
--[GOKU] Hm?
But you can't help it! After
all, you're Goku's son!
[GOKU sighs]
[CHICHI] It's family tradition,
pure and simple!
[ALL laugh]
[shutter clicks]
[GOHAN GOKU]
[NARRATOR] That night, the sound
of laughter could be heard
coming from a small house
deep in the woods.
It could still be heard
echoing through the valley
in the wee hours
of the morning.
Inside, the room was
aglow with the love
that is shared between
family and friends.
It was a night to
remember for all.
But a vigil of a different
kind was being kept elsewhere.
Oblivious to the beauty of the
sparkling sky above him,
Cell was waiting.
Don't miss the next
Dragon Ball Z!