Ready? And go!
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z...
The training on King
Kai's planet intensified,
as an impatient
Piccolo challenged
Yamcha, Tien, and Chiaotzu to a
grueling 3-on-1 sparring match!
[NARRATOR] And Goku did
some training of his own,
pushing himself
to the limits
by increasing the gravity
level inside his ship
as he raced to join
his friends on Namek...
You have
proven yourself...
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Krillin
received a Dragon Ball
from Guru, the eldest Namek,
while Gohan
searched for another
with the help of
the Dragon Radar.
[NARRATOR] Though
weak from battle,
Vegeta was far from finished
as he not only escaped
from Frieza's minions,
he also put
into motion
a plan to take the
Dragon Balls for himself!
[ZARBON] He's gone!
Go now! Do you
hear me Zarbon?!
I'll find him!
[NARRATOR]
The adventure continues!
[ZARBON] Vegeta! Vegeta,
where are you, Saiyan?!
Believe me, as soon as
I get my hands on you,
I'm going to rip
you to pieces!
[FRIEZA] Haven't found him
yet, have you Zarbon?
Just remember, you have
one hour to find him
before I hold you completely
responsible for his escape!
[VEGETA laughing]
[VEGETA] Like you
could ever find me...
Well, now let's see.
Five Dragon Balls,
just waiting
to be stolen...
What would be the best way
to get them out of here?
Well, with Frieza and Zarbon
busy looking for me,
at least I have the element
of surprise on my side.
Come to think of it...
[VEGETA] That might be
all I need to escape...
Yes!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA grunting]
[growling]
[VEGETA] There...
That should be enough.
[VEGETA] Hey! Are you
guys looking for someone?
[FRIEZA gasps]
Wait! What was that?!
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA] Rraagh!
[ZARBON yelling]
How dare you!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Rraugh!
Hyaah!
It sounded
like the blast
was coming from this
direction, down the corridor!
[FRIEZA growling]
No! Stop him!
He can't be allowed to
get near the Dragon Balls!
Hraaugh!
[VEGETA] Huh! Urrgh!
[VEGETA] Haah!
[VEGETA] There now.
That ought to do it.
[BOTH gasp]
[FRIEZA] My Dragon Balls!
Where are my Dragon Balls?!
[ZARBON screaming]
Vegeta!
He couldn't have
gone that far...
[FRIEZA] What are you
waiting for, you fool?!
Don't you think you've
disappointed me enough
for one day? Get out of my
sight! Go find him! Now!
[ZARBON] Yes, Lord!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[thinking] If I fly away,
they'll be sure to see me.
I can slip away
unnoticed down here.
[thinking] Now to find where
those Dragon Balls landed...
[FRIEZA] Stop apologizing and
start doing things right!
You're a disgrace of a warrior!
You're not fit to serve me!
I can't believe I
ever counted on you
to take care of anything
important for me!
Now my Dragon Balls are
stolen and Vegeta is missing.
Have I left anything
out, Zarbon?
No.
[FRIEZA] Well, you'd
just better hope
you can get those
Dragon Balls back for me.
You have one hour.
Don't disappoint me again!
[FRIEZA growls]
Yes, Lord!
[screaming]
[beeping]
Let's see...
Over that way.
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] Oh no...
[GOHAN] Dead...
They're all dead...
[GOHAN whimpers]
Vegeta! How could
you do this?
[crackling]
Hello? Is
someone here?
The wind...
[GOHAN] He destroyed
everything!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN] I swear you'll
pay for this, Vegeta!
You'll pay for
what you've done!
[VEGETA gasps]
[panting]
[panting continues]
Now, with any luck, they should
be around here somewhere.
[VEGETA laughs]
Well, how
about that?!
Five Dragon Balls all
lined up in a row...
Sometimes I even
impress myself.
[VEGETA] With the one I hid
in the lake, that makes six.
Just one
more to find!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Once I've
collected all seven,
everyone in this entire
universe will tremble
and fall to their
knees before me.
[VEGETA chuckles]
Great, someone's
coming! Is it Zarbon?
No, the power level's not
quite as strong as Zarbon's.
[VEGETA gasps]
So, they are here...
[KRILLIN laughs]
I can't wait!
Oh man, Gohan's
gonna be so excited
when he hears that Guru can make
him even stronger than ever!
That Earthling Krillin... But,
how'd he get to Planet Namek?
Oh well, at
least I know where
the last
Dragon Ball is.
[VEGETA laughs]
Guess I should
thank you
for finding it for
me, puny Earthman!
[VEGETA laughs]
[GOHAN grunting]
That was the
last one...
[GOHAN] I promise...
Me and my friends
will try to bring all
of you back if we can.
Well, now. I'd better go
and find that Dragon Ball.
[radar beeping]
[GOHAN] Hmm...
[beeping continues]
Uh! Wha...? Could it...
Could it be here in the lake?
[GOHAN]
I think... it is!
So now all I have to do is just
swim down there and find it!
All right!
I found you...
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOKU] 9994...
9995... 9996...
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU] 9997... I gotta
make it to 10,000,
then I can up the gravity
level to 60. Come on!
Aaargh!
9,998...
9,999...
10 thou--
[GOKU panting heavily]
[GOKU grunting]
[grunting continues]
I... I can't move! I can't
be this tired already.
[GOKU grunting]
All right!
It won't be long now!
Well, I see that
little worm is
trying to collect the
Dragon Balls too.
As if he
stands a chance
against the likes
of Frieza and myself.
Oh well, I guess it can't
hurt to try. Or will it!
[VEGETA laughs]
Damn! Where is he?
Where is that puny Saiyan?
If I only had my scouter, I
could find him in a heartbeat...
[ZARBON growls]
What the--!
I swear I heard something...
If I don't locate him, I'll
have to answer to Lord Frieza!
[ZARBON gasps]
It's Vegeta!
Wait... It's the weakling
who saved that little Namek.
Where did HE get
a Dragon Ball?!
I'm sure Vegeta must
be somewhere nearby.
[ZARBON gasps]
You're not getting
away! Not this time!
[VEGETA] Huh?
[VEGETA] I get the feeling I'm
being followed... Zarbon...
Well, let that
freak follow me.
I'll take care of
him as well.
I'd bet anything he's still
cocky from our last fight.
He has no idea that defeating
a Saiyan makes the Saiyan
grow even stronger!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU] C'mon... All I
need is one more...
[grunting continues]
[DR. BRIEF] This is crazy!
Huh? Hey!
Dr. Brief!
Son, you're nuts
if you think
you can workout in
100 times gravity!
But I'm only working out
in 50 times normal gravity.
Unless your gravity
machine is on the blink...
Impossible! There's nothing
wrong with my Gravitron!
[GOKU] Are you sure?
[DR. BRIEF] Just a second...
[DR. BRIEF] I better
recalculate my calculations...
Yes! That's it!
[GOKU grunting]
I think I
figured it out.
Uh, Goku, the
Gravitron is unstable
because you're in
a magnetic storm.
I'm afraid you're going
to have to put up with it
until the
storm passes.
[GOKU] So there's
nothing I can do?
[DR. BRIEF]
No. Just ride it out.
The storm should only
last about an hour.
[GOKU] An hour!? I don't
think I can last that long!
I'd say you're
probably right,
but just try to hang
in there anyway, okay?
Gee, thanks for that
vote of confidence, Doc!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] Wooaahh...
Aaahhh...
[GOKU yelling]
[BULMA screams]
Bulma?
[BULMA whimpering]
[growling]
[BULMA] How many times have
I told you?! Don't do that!
But-but Bulma,
you and I both know that
it's far too dangerous to
be out in the open.
They'll spot
us for sure.
Hey... I'm a big girl,
and I'll do what I want!
Krillin, is that the...
the Dragon Ball?
Yeah, it sure is!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Wow... The Dragon Balls on
this planet sure are big!
[KRILLIN] It was a gift from the
eldest Namek... His name's Guru.
Hey, Bulma!
So where's Gohan?
Is he in the
cave? Get him!
I want to take the two
of you to meet Guru!
Sorry. The little
squirt went off
to find another
Dragon Ball.
After you left, we saw
another one on the radar,
near the village
Vegeta destroyed.
B-But do think
he's safe?
Oh, no! A huge power level...
Coming right for us!
Stop your worrying!
It's just Gohan!
No...
It's not Gohan!
[BOTH] It's Vegeta!!
[BOTH whimpering]
[thinking] Dammit!
I was so excited about
my new strength
that I didn't even notice
I was being followed!
Well, the surprises just
don't stop, do they?
I've found a couple of
Earthlings far from home
with no one around
to save them.
[BOTH whimpering]
[VEGETA] And it
appears that you have
just what I'm looking for...
Hand over the
Dragon Ball or die!
Come on! Don't do
anything stupid.
Just hand it over.
And I wouldn't attempt to
escape with it either,
because if you tried
something like that...
The sniveling girl behind you
would suffer the consequences.
Now, hand over
that ball.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[VEGETA] Looks like
we have company.
[ZARBON chuckles]
Wow! He's cute!
I'll bet with his
brawny good looks,
he's come here
to rescue me!
Not even close!
[NARRATOR] Zarbon has finally
caught up with Vegeta,
and one more Dragon Ball to
add to Frieza's collection.
And before
the showdown
between these two
villains has even begun,
Bulma and Krillin are already
caught in the crossfire!
Meanwhile, Goku
struggles to survive
the lethal levels of gravity
caused by a magnetic storm!
Will our hero ever make
it to Planet Namek alive?
Don't miss the next
Dragon Ball Z!