[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
Bulma, Krillin, and
Gohan set out on a quest
for the Dragon Balls
on Planet Namek.
But on the way, they ran into
some big trouble... Literally!
Oh no!
Bulma!
[NARRATOR] An in-flight
collision should have
spelled doom for the young
travelers, but instead
they found themselves
mysteriously transported
into the belly of
an alien vessel,
where danger lurked
at every turn!
[squealing]
[BULMA screaming]
[LITTLE BOY]
Don't move!
[GOHAN]
Don't hurt her!
Just stay there!
I don't wanna get shot!
Easy now, everyone. We're
not trying to hurt anybody.
[NARRATOR] Now, our heroes
have been surrounded
by what appears to be a
well-equipped army of children!
Who will make the first move
in this bizarre standoff?
Find out next,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[BULMA panting]
[BULMA whimpering]
Ah...!
Huh?
[GOHAN] Please, listen!
We can explain.
You must have us confused
with someone else.
We're from the planet
Earth. We're friendly!
[GIRL wailing]
I don't want to hear your
bogus explanations any more!
Hey, guys c'mon
now... Wait a minute!
We have nothing
against you!
You attacked us so we
had to defend ourselves!
You gotta
believe me!
Ah, shut up!
[KRILLIN shouting]
[BULMA] Hey! Why don't you two
try being quiet for a change?!
You're gonna get
us all killed!
Easy now, kids... I'm not
trying to hurt anyone.
[KRILLIN] Gohan,
let's power up.
Right.
[GOHAN and KRILLIN growling]
[BOYS gasping]
[KRILLIN chuckling]
Uh?
[KRILLIN] Ow! Ow-ow-ow-ow!
Hey!
What was that?!
[BOY]
Don't move!
Or I'll shoot
you... I swear!
Zeshin, why don't you just
kill them all right now?!
We know they must be
allies with Frieza!
Uh, okay.
You three shouldn't have
come here... I'm sorry.
[ALL screaming]
What's happening?!
We're in big
trouble, sir!
We just entered a
huge asteroid field!
Hey! Keep an eye
on those three!
And if they do
anything strange,
you have my permission
to shoot 'em!
[RADAR GIRL whimpering]
Ahh!
[screaming]
[BULMA] Hey, Krillin!
Quick! Come get me
out of this thing!
[KRILLIN] Ready, Gohan?
I'm ready!
[GOKU screaming]
Please!
Don't do it!
[screaming continues]
[GOKU screaming]
I haven't
stuck you yet!
Oh boy... Goku,
please don't tell me
that I'm going to have
to start training you
not to fear needles.
[GOKU screaming]
Didn't you hear me before?
I haven't even stuck you yet!
Hmph!
What a little baby!
Screaming and crying
over a tiny needle!
I can't even remember
Gohan whining this much
when he
was born.
How pathetic. My own husband
can fight in epic battles
to save the world,
yet cries over a shot!
[GOKU whining]
Hmph! Goku,
you're on your own.
I have more important
things I need to do.
[GOKU] ChiChi, wait!
[DOCTOR] Now, I promise...
You won't feel a thing!
[GOKU screaming]
[rumbling]
[screaming]
[crying]
[GOHAN] Uhh...
[BULMA] Huh?!
Hey guys!
Let's keep moving!
[KRILLIN] But...
We are in the middle
of an asteroid field!
No ship can take
a direct hit,
especially with those
kids behind the controls!
Now, let's go!
But, Bulma, wait! We can't just
leave them here like this!
They're scared!
And if we don't get outta
here, we'll be dead!
[BULMA screaming]
[GOHAN whimpering]
[screaming]
[BULMA screams]
[GOHAN and KRILLIN grunting]
You guys okay?
Uhh... Uh-huh...
Good!
What's going
on in here?!
[explosion, screaming]
Help us!
Just follow me!
I'll take
care of it!
Great... Why do they always
have to be such heroes?
[BULMA screaming]
Hey! Who in the world
is flying this thing?!
Hey! You don't even know
what you're doing! Move it!
Who do you
think you are?!
I'm a pilot! Which means
I DO know what I'm doing.
I think she's a
dirty liar, Boon!
[BOON] I know how to
fly this ship!
If you want
to live,
then you're gonna let me
pilot this piece of junk!
Okay, so we've got the
fuel indicator,
and controls for
the lateral jets...
Where is the
speed control?
Look! Either you tell me,
or we're all history!
It's the one
on the left.
Okay. Got it!
[GIRL screaming]
[GOHAN] Haah!
[screaming continues]
Wow!
I thought we were gone
there for a second.
[guns cocking]
Aah!
Nice! I save
your lives,
and what do I get in
return? Guns in my face!
Yeah, 'cause we still
don't trust you!
And how could we?
You and your friends
are responsible
for destroying
our home!
[BULMA] Look, I think
this is all a big mix-up!
So tell me... what friends
are you talking about?
Don't pretend
you don't know!
We're talking about your
homicidal buddy named Frieza!
Frieza?
Bulma!
[BULMA] Krillin, Gohan,
tell them.
These kids... They think we
know some guy named Frieza.
We don't think, lady!
We know who you are!
Just look at how strong
your two brothers are!
They think
we're brothers!
No way.
Listen, you've got
this all wrong.
Those two are not
my brothers!
And don't accuse us of
being friends with somebody
that we don't
even know!
[KRILLIN] Bulma, wait!
I say we throw these liars
out of the airlock! Now!
[ZESHIN]
I don't think so.
Zeshin?
It's all right, everyone.
You can put your weapons down.
Have you lost
your mind?!
These three are
allies with Frieza!
We have to treat them
like a serious threat
and eliminate them!
If they're allies
with Frieza,
explain to me why
they chose to help us.
They would have killed us just
like he killed our parents.
These people actually
care about us.
They aren't like
Frieza and his men!
They wouldn't
attack us
in the middle of the
night without warning us!
Get to safety!
Leave us behind!
I remember...
Run, Boon!
[remembering]
Mother! Father, no!
Hide before
they see you!
[screaming]
[evil laughter]
[yelling]
I... think we
can trust them.
Boon?
Well, I'm glad you
guys believe us now.
I wonder if the
people who attacked
with Frieza
were Saiyans?
Hey, do you remember if
the people that conquered
your planet had tails that
came out about this far?
A tail? I didn't see
a tail on any of them.
Oh. Well, so much for that
brilliant theory, Krillin.
That means there's a group
of warriors out there
even more evil
than Saiyans.
What kind of a planet
did you live on?
I mean
before Frieza?
Our planet
was successful.
A truly wonderful and
peaceful place to live.
Until that
terrible night!
When they took
our innocence...
[screaming]
[ZESHIN] It was an ambush.
We never even saw them coming.
When they arrived they
said the planet
now belonged
to Frieza
and anyone who didn't name
him as ruler would be killed.
Most of the people gave in and
professed Frieza as their King,
but the invaders had no
intention of allowing us
to live in the
first place.
They murdered everyone who
came across their path.
Women, children... There was
no limit to the carnage.
It was terrible.
It must have been very
difficult for you to escape.
The few adults who realized
Frieza's true intentions
were able to
cover long enough
for their kids to
make an escape.
Those that were lucky enough to
make it to their ships in time
were eventually
destroyed in space.
We only avoided
being destroyed
because of our
mirrored exterior.
This ship has mirrors
on the outside?
That explains why you
showed up on radar,
yet we couldn't actually
see you with our eyes.
Your people must have
brilliant scientific minds
to create
such a ship.
So, where in the galaxy
are you headed to now?
Anywhere specific?
That's right.
There is a planet
that my father
used to visit
from time to time for
trading purposes.
And I just know that
they will be willing
to accept us
without question.
Is this
planet far?
Yes it is. But we're willing,
even if it takes years.
Ha, ha!
[BOTH chuckling]
Well, good luck
to all of you.
Thanks, guys.
And same to you.
We'll see ya!
[CHILDREN laughing]
Let's go,
boys.
We have a lot of
time to make up,
thanks to this
little detour.
It's okay,
Bulma.
It's not like Namek
is gonna go anywhere.
Wait a minute...
You three are all trying
to get to the planet Namek?
Sure are.
You've heard of it?
I think we passed it
around 2 or 3 weeks ago.
If you head in the
direction of K-5162,
you'll find about a 10
day shortcut to Namek.
A shortcut?
U-Uh-huh.
So head towards K-5162,
huh? Thank you! Let's go!
[GOHAN chuckling]
Ah! If you take the
shortcut, don't forget--
[BOON] That was an
interesting visit.
Huh, Zeshin?
They turned out to be
nice people after all.
Yeah.
Well... We should
get going ourselves!
Sounds good!
You guys ready?
[cheering]
Navigate to planet Namek
through the K-5162 system.
I'm glad they
mentioned that shortcut.
What's the matter?
Oh, I was just wondering
who this Frieza guy is
they kept
talking about.
Well, they said the attackers
weren't Saiyans, right?
It just sounded like
something Saiyans would do.
Just forget about
it, Krillin!
Try to get
some sleep.
I'll see you guys...
Whenever I wake up.
[SUBORDINATE 1]
Hey, look.
[siren beeping]
[SUBORDINATE 2]
Something's coming.
[beeping continues]
[SUBORDINATE 1] Is it Frieza?!
[SUBORDINATE 2] No! That's
impossible.
I think I recognize
that signal.
Of course!
It's Vegeta.
Well, that's
strange, isn't it?
Something must
have happened...
I never got an
arrival report.
Yes... Control
tower, come in.
Vegeta is here.
Prepare for his arrival.
Look! Up there!
There's only one
pod! Where's Nappa?
What is he doing?
He should be out by now!
I'm receiving a very low
life-force reading on him.
What?!
[SUBORDINATE D] Why, he's using
his life support system!
[SUBORDINATE E] Quick! Let's get
him to the treatment center.
[rumbling]
What was that?!
Don't know!
[GOHAN and KRILLIN whimpering]
[KRILLIN] Bulma! Something's
happening to the ship!
[BULMA] Don't worry,
Krillin.
This shortcut takes us through
a recently exploded nebula.
It's just a storm in space.
Don't be a wimp.
I mean really,
how can she sleep
through all
this shaking?
[screaming]
[thunder]
[distant thunder]
I think
it stopped.
[BULMA] Huh?
Uh?
[KRILLIN] Uhh...
[bonk]
That was really
uncalled for, Bulma!
Don't you ever lay your hands
on me again while I'm sleeping!
No, Bulma! It looked a lot
worse than it really was.
I know what I saw!
And I'm sure I
didn't fall asleep
while lying
in Krillin's lap!
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA laughing]
Woah, that looks
like it hurts a lot.
[BULMA] Guys!
Check this out!
Yes! It's Namek!
We finally made it!
That sure was a fast
trip, huh, guys?
If it weren't for
that shortcut,
we'd only be
halfway there.
Are you
sure that's...
Planet Namek?
Trust me, it's the
right planet!
Now, let's go and find
those Dragon Balls!
[NARRATOR] Bulma believes they
have arrived at planet Namek,
though Krillin and Gohan
have their doubts.
They're about to discover
whose hunch is correct
as they prepare for their
landing. What mysteries await?
Find out, on the
next Dragon Ball Z!