[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
power levels were
shooting off the charts,
as Frieza and Goku exchanged
punches, kicks, and insults.
While thanks to some
clever wishing,
Bulma and the gang found
themselves safe and sound
on planet Earth.
But where is Goku?
He's still battling
it out with Frieza.
Wanting to put an end to the
evil tyrant once and for all,
Goku chose to remain on Namek.
A brave move indeed,
because the damaged planet
is set to explode any minute!
And it seems Frieza
has a plan of his own.
[FRIEZA] I don't know how
to break this to you,
but you only have about
one minute to live.
[NARRATOR] Can Super Saiyan
Goku finally defeat Frieza
and escape from
Namek in time?
Find out today!
[GOKU &amp; FRIEZA grunting]
What makes you think
you can do this to me?
You're nothing but
an overgrown monkey!
[GOKU growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[KING KAI] Goku! You
don't have time for this!
[TIEN] What is it, King Kai?
What's happening?
[KING KAi] On the surface,
it is an even battle.
Goku is matching every
move that Frieza makes!
[KING KAI] But in one minute,
none of that will matter...
Huh?
And the battle
will end precisely
as Frieza has planned it.
What? What are you saying?
No one has ever truly
challenged Frieza before!
Until now, he has
gotten everything
he could wrap his
icy fingers around.
When it became clear that
Goku could not be defeated,
Frieza was stunned!
So he did something drastic!
Your power is amazing
but there's more to
winning than that!
Sometimes it's the smartest
one who wins, not the strongest!
[FRIEZA laughs]
Now, say goodbye to Namek!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[KING KAI] Out of desperation,
Frieza shot an energy blast
down to Namek's core,
attempting to explode
the entire planet!
[GOKU yells]
[KING KAI] With Namek
reduced to space dust,
Goku and everyone else on the
planet would surely be doomed!
[BULMA screams]
[GOHAN screams]
Whoa! This is huge!
[KING KAI] Fortunately,
things didn't work out
like Frieza had planned.
Darn! I held back
too much power!
So you couldn't do it!
You just couldn't go
through with it after all!
You couldn't kill us both!
You still don't get it, do you?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] I didn't plan on
destroying myself,
just you and the planet!
I can breathe in space
and you can't!
That means if the planet goes...
then you won't have
anymore air to live on!
And I shall be victorious!
Five minutes!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA] Then the
planet explodes!
Most of the five
minutes have expired!
Unless Goku hurries,
he will have no choice but
to die with the planet!
But Frieza will survive!
He can live anywhere.
[CHIAOTZU gasps]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[blows landing,
grunting]
You see?
A Saiyan can't beat me!
A monkey can't beat me!
You can't! You can't! You can't!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
I hate you!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA screams]
[birds chirping]
Um, what are you doing
with those leaves?
[BULMA giggles]
I'm telling fortunes.
I used to do this
when I was a child.
[BULMA] When you want a traveler
to come home, you draw a circle,
you put three leaves in the
middle, and then you burn them.
If all three leaves burn up,
then the traveler will
return home safely!
So... this will tell
us if Goku's okay, right?
[BULMA gasps]
Huh?
[NAMEKS murmuring]
[BULMA] Look! They're burning!
I'm sure they'll all burn up!
[DENDE] So Goku
will come back safe?
Of course! The leaves
have never been wrong!
[BULMA gasps]
--Huh?!
--[NAMEKS gasp]
[BULMA sighs]
[GOHAN] Fortune telling
is nonsense!
I know my Dad will
make it home okay!
Hmph.
Yeah, you're right!
He's going to finish
Frieza for good,
and come back to Mom and me!
[FRIEZA yells]
[BOTH grunt]
Huh?!
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[grunting continues]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA growls]
You may be strong, but you're
still just a stupid animal!
[GOKU grunts,
FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU screams]
[FRIEZA yells]
See?! Just a beast!
--[GOKU] Frieza...
--What!?
[GOKU] I'd rather
be a brainless beast
than a heartless monster...
like you!
You fool!
[FRIEZA yells]]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA rasps]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
Huh...?
[GOKU shouts]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[growling continues]
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA] You think this is
funny? Toying with me?!
[FRIEZA yells
[GOKU &amp; FRIEZA grunting]
[GOKU] No, Frieza, there's
nothing funny about this.
[GOKU grunts]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] All that you've done to
me, I'll pay you back ten times!
No! A thousand times!
[FRIEZA] Oh yes,
stupid Saiyan...
Ahhh!
You will pay for this!
It's done.
Uh, what do you mean?
[KING KAI] It's done?
So... how did it end?
[thinking] Maybe Goku
is wiser than I thought...
[FRIEZA] Don't just stand
there! Say something!
You said it's done.
What do you mean?
Your energy level is
decreasing with every blow.
In fact, you're not even a
challenge to me anymore.
It wouldn't be fair for me
to keep fighting you.
I'm satisfied now. Your pride
has been torn to shreds.
You've challenged and lost to a
fighter who is superior to you,
and to make it worse...
He's just a monkey, right?
[FRIEZA whimpers]
It would be meaningless
to fight you now,
you're too scared and ashamed.
Live with the shock! Keep it
bottled up inside you silently.
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU] Goodbye, Frieza.
Never do mischief again.
May you live the rest
of your life in peace.
[FRIEZA growls]
"Peace"?
Nonsense!
[FRIEZA growls]
Never!
I will never... never be...
...defeated!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
You truly are a helpless fool!
I gave you one last
chance to live!
[GOKU] And this
is how you repay me?!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Round and round
the monkey goes!
If he should stop,
then off with his nose!
[FRIEZA laughs]
I just don't understand you,
Frieza. I tried to help you.
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Huh...?
Huh! It seems the little
Saiyan has a strategy!
Fly at me and pull up
at the last second,
so the blade will
cut me instead!
You think I'm stupid enough to
fall for such a childish trick?!
Goku, you're wasting your time!
This is your last
chance to escape!
Huh?
Come home, Daddy!
[NARRATOR] Can Goku outsmart
the diabolical Frieza
and avoid this final attack?
Tune in for the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!