[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
Babidi and Dabura
took a major step
toward reviving the
terrible Majin Buu.
But when the wizard realized
he still had only half
the pure energy he needed to
awaken his sleeping monster,
he sent his henchmen to
gather the rest.
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
this would prove to be
a difficult task indeed.
Something PuiPui found
out the hard way!
[NARRATOR] And when the
light-eating monster Yakon
tried to rob Goku of his
Super-Saiyan power,
Goku gave the beast a little
more than he bargained for...
[YAKON roars]
[GOKU growls]
[YAKON grunts]
Dabura...
Who will protect me?
I will be the warrior
they must battle.
[NARRATOR] With Goku
and the gang getting closer,
Babidi's back is to the wall.
Fortunately for him, he's still
got Dabura on his side.
The demon king has retired to
his mediation chamber
to increase his
fierce fighting spirit.
[BABIDI]
Good!
Soon he'll be ready to go
crush the three intruders...
I can hardly wait.
[JEWL yells]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, on the
other side of the planet,
the Battle Royale continues...
Five fighters--
No, make that three!
Three fighters locked
in an all-out battle
for the tournament title!
The last one standing
will be named
the Number-One-Under-The-Sun.
Trunks and Goten, posing as the
mysterious Mighty Mask,
have their hands and feet
busy trying to block
the furious fists of
Krillin's wife, Number 18.
It's a ferocious fight and
whoever wins will go on
to face Mr. Satan.
Will this be the day that
Mr. Satan is exposed
for the fraud he really is?
Stay tuned and find out!
Where are they?
Sleeping?
After those moves
you and Dad showed off
for the last two stages?
You probably scared them off!
I hope they don't all run away.
You haven't had your turn!
[SUPREME KAI whimpers]
[GOHAN grunts]
[giggles]
Very soon...
Dabura's fighting spirit
is rising! I can feel it!
[laughs]
Now that Dabura is
taking care of Stage Three,
Majin Buu will be free
in no time at all!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] How about this,
Ladies and Gentlemen?!
Neither Mighty Mask nor Number
18 are showing any signs
of slowing down!
[BOTH grunt]
I'm still not sure how
those two are fighting
in mid-air like that,
but I am sure of this!
Whenever they invented
the Battle Royale,
this is the kind of
action they had in mind!
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[gasps]
[TRUNKS, GOTEN grunting]
[TRUNKS]
Oh no!
[GOTEN]
Come on, Trunks!
Land a punch, would ya?!
[TRUNKS]
I'm trying, Goten! I'm trying!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[grunts]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[GOTEN]
Yeah! That's the way, Trunks!
Oh my! I wonder if Number 18
will be joining Killa and Jewl
over in the infirmary?!
[JEWL whimpers]
[KILLA groans]
As you know, there's a lot
riding on this fight!
The winner will face the
current champ Mr. Satan!
[MR. SATAN snarls]
[gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
[growling]
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH grunting]
--[CROWD gasping]
--Ohh...!
Aw, wow! I've never seen
anything like that!
[CHICHI, BULMA, MARON cheering]
[TRUNKS growls]
[GOTEN] I don't think the
crowd likes us, Trunks...
Hey don't blame me,
blame her!
I'm doing the
best I can up here!
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[TRUNKS, GOTEN grunting]
[CROWD murmuring]
[BOTH grunting]
What a fighter! She's great!
[whimpers] Look at them go...
I can't beat them...
[BOTH grunting]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[TRUNKS growls]
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
His arms and legs are so small,
but he's very strong.
I wonder what his secret is?
[TRUNKS growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[ANDROID 18]
Raagh!
[GOTEN grunts]
Boy, Goten, this girl
is really tough...
She's a lot stronger than
Krillin that's for sure!
[GOTEN] You've gotta
try harder, Trunks!
Hey! You haven't even
landed one kick yet!
You try harder!
I would, but I can't
see a thing down here!
This isn't the time
to argue, okay?!
I'll tell you what, if you land
a kick I'll buy you an extra toy
or something with
the prize money.
[GOTEN]
Oh really?! All right!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[GOTEN]
Okay, let's do it!
[ANDROID 18 growls]
Are you ready, Goten?!
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
--[TRUNKS, GOTEN yell]
--[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[grunting]
[GOTEN yelling]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[grunting]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
Strange...
I'm having a hard time
anticipating his movements!
[GOTEN] Trunks, that was a
great punch you threw!
Hey, it's not over yet!
[TRUNKS growls]
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[grunting]
Mama?
She's in trouble...
Come on!
You can do it, Number 18!
Oh no! Somebody
please stop them...
Stop them for me!
Great! We're winning!
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
[GOTEN growls]
[grunting]
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[TRUNKS screams]
[ANDROID 18 snarls]
[GOTEN, TRUNKS yell]
[yells]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[screams, grunts]
Is... Is he dead?
[MR. SATAN grunting]
What was I thinking?!
"Hey, let's do a Battle Royale!"
Why couldn't I just
keep my big mouth shut?!
[grunts]
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[CROWD gasping]
[MR. SATAN grunts]
A-hem!
Hey! Look at me,
I'm still in the game!
[CROWD gasping]
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
[TRUNKS groans]
[GOTEN]
Ugh... Are you okay, Trunks?
[TRUNKS]
That was a heckuva fall!
Yeah... Let's switch now...
Let me be on top now, okay?
Well, uh, sure then, okay.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN grunt]
Uh? Hello there, Mighty Mask...
Have you thought
about giving up?
[ANNOUNCER yelps]
Ha, ha! I never give up!
[gasps]
Wow! He's back up!
That's fantastic!
How'd he do that?!
Mighty Mask is a mighty
impressive fighter,
that's for sure.
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
[GOTEN grunts]
[GOTEN growls]
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
What happened?!
His technique has
changed drastically!
[TRUNKS]
Now! Go for it, Goten!
[GOTEN]
Hm.
[GOTEN yells]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
--All right!
--[TRUNKS] Great!
Now let's finish this!
Okay!
[ANDROID 18 yells, growls]
[gasps]
[ALL grunting]
Gotcha! [yells]
[ANDROID 18 snarls]
Aaahh!
[GOTEN gasps]
[TRUNKS]
That was a close one!
Yeah, you gotta move
pretty fast up here, don't ya?
Something is definitely
not right about this guy!
Mama! Do your best!
I know you can win!
Right. I will win.
[chuckles]
I can sense that Dabura
is almost ready.
[giggles] Good! Good!
Dabura is going to rid me
of those annoying intruders,
but first I must have
their energy
so I can feed it to Majin Buu.
He's the perfect choice to
handle all the dirty work.
After all, he's had so
much experience at it.
[DABURA laughs]
[BABIDI thinking] And the more
he concentrates his evil spirit
in that meditation room,
the easier it will be for me
to manipulate him!
[laughs]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[grunting]
[CROWD gasping]
Go, mama!
[ANDROID 18 yelling]
Hey, Trunks! Look at her eyes!
She looks pretty mad!
Don't worry about
that right now!
Just fight back
or else we're history!
[GOTEN]
Hey, wait a minute!
Why do I have to
do all the work?!
[ANDROID 18 yells]
[TRUNKS]
Oh no! Goten!
[ANDROID 18 yells]
[BOTH scream]
Oh...
Oh! Mighty Mask
has hit the ground!
I don't know if he'll be able
to get back up this time!
That leaves only Number 18 and
Mr. Satan to duke it out
for the Tournament Title!
[GOTEN groans]
[TRUNKS] You gotta look
where you're going Goten!
Now move it!
I'm on top again!
[TRUNKS, GOTEN grunting]
Uh... Are you giving up
this time, Mighty Mask?
[screams]
Ladies and gentlemen,
Mighty Mask has gotten up again!
This is a perseverance
he's not shown
at any of his previous
Tournament appearances!
It's hard to think of this
as a Battle Royale anymore...
It has now become
an all-out war between
Mighty Mask and Number 18!
But... what about me?
[CROWD gasping]
It's... amazing!
[yells]
Heads up, Goten!
[screams]
[ANNOUNCER grunts]
[ANNOUNCER]
Huh...?
[MR. SATAN]
G-Guh...?
[laughs]
We can't win like this!
[GOTEN] Then let's go
Super Saiyan, Trunks!
What do you say?!
Yeah! Good plan!
With this suit on,
nobody even knows who we are..
Let's do it!
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
Goten, you ready?
[GOTEN]
Yup!
--[TRUNKS yells]
--[GOTEN growls]
[gasps]
What's happening?
What's that light?
[ROSHI]
Hmm!
What's wrong with him?
He's glowing!
Now we're gonna settle
this once and for all.
And this time, Goten,
we're gonna win.
[GOTEN] I sure hope
you're right, Trunks.
She's pretty tough!
Listen... We'll be fine.
I'll watch your back and
you watch mine, okay?
I get it.
A couple of Super Saiyans.
That explains everything.
Well, now they're mine.
[GOTEN] Okay, Trunks,
I'm ready when you are.
All right! Here we go!
[gasps]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[CROWD gasping]
[MR. SATAN gasps, sighs]
So she knows...
Rats! I missed her!
[GOTEN]
Come on, let's keep going!
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
They're not joking around...
That energy blast would have
blown up this entire stadium!
Maybe I've been
underestimating them.
They could be dangerous!
I'd better end this match now
before it really gets
out of control.
I think it's time you
let me win, Trunks and Goten!
--[GOTEN gasps]
--Aw, man! We're busted!
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[TRUNKS yells]
--[yells]
--[TRUNKS screams]
[GOTEN screams]
[BOTH yell]
[screams] Oh no! Mighty Mask
has been sliced in half!
[TRUNKS]
Great! Way to go, Goten!
Why'd you have to go that way?!
Oh yeah?! I could say
the same to you!
Hey! Look! Is that Goten?!
What's he doing way up there?!
That means the other one
must be Trunks!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[ROSHI thinking] I knew it
was those two all along!
Ohh! What should
we do now, Trunks?
Goten! We've got to
finish this match!
Let's go!
[gasps]
[BOTH yell]
[ALL grunting]
Hey! The two of you
can't fight together!
You're disqualified!
Do you hear me?!
Uh-oh. I think we're in trouble.
Me too... Should we go?
Uh-huh...
[TRUNKS]
Your tournament was stupid!
Hey! Goten!
Where are you going?!
Yeah! Trunks!
Get back here now!
[sighs]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Wow.
Number 18's done it!
Mighty Mask was disqualified
because he was two people!
And that means Mr. Satan and
Number 18 are the last fighters!
One of them will be
declared the champ!
[CROWD cheering]
Go, Mom! You're the best!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
What'll I do?
I'll be a goner if I fight
this girl all by myself!
[GOKU yawns]
What time is it?
Gosh, I really wish
they'd hurry up!
[BABIDI]
Hmmm...?
Dabura!
[DABURA chuckles]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[NARRATOR]
Uh-oh!
Dabura has come out of his
meditation chamber,
100% charged and ready to fight!
Gohan's anxious for his
challenger to step through
the door,
but is he ready to face
the King of the
Demon World himself?
And back at the
Battle Royale,
Number 18 has her sights set on
Mr. Satan's championship title.
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[NARRATOR] It's gonna be
showdown of epic proportions.
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!