[PICCOLO and GOKU yell]
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
Goku and Piccolo launched
a combined assault
against the
evil Raditz!
But in spite of their
fierce efforts,
Raditz easily deflected
their every attack,
and countered with
an energy blast
that sent Goku and
Piccolo reeling!
Having firmly seized
the upper hand,
Raditz proceeded to deal out
a series of punishing blows!
And the mighty Goku
was rendered helpless
as his older brother cruelly
ground him into the dust.
Time to die!
[beeping]
Huh?
[NARRATOR]
That's right... It's Gohan!
What awesome new powers
have been awakened
within Goku's son?
The answer... Today!
Eh?!
[gasps]
[RADITZ] You?
I don't believe it!
[PICCOLO] Goku! Look over by
the crater... It's your son!
It can't be...
[GOKU] Gohan?
Gohan, Daddy can't
get up right now.
Run away
from here!
[grunts] Run away! Gohan!
[GOKU] Run now!
[RADITZ] Ahh!
Power Level 1370?
Impossible for a kid!
And, and it's
still going up!
[gasps]
Leave my Dad...
...alone!
[GOHAN screams]
[RADITZ groans]
[PICCOLO] Whaaa?
What the...
G-Gohan?
Uh, Daddy?
Gohan...
Go...
Get out of here...
But, Daddy...
[RADITZ] No one's ever
done that to me!
No...
Stay back!
Gohan, you
have to go!
[beeping]
Gohan... Quick!
Run now!
What? Hey, kid...
What happened to all
that power you had?
[GOHAN] Wha...
What power?
Bah! Play dumb
if you want.
You'll pay
all the same!
Daddy...
Help.
Leave him alone!
[RADTIZ yells]
Gohan!
[GOKU]
Huh?!
Please Don't hurt him.
He's just a boy!
Yes, he's just a little
boy, that's true!
But he's
very strong,
and he has
a power level
even higher than
yours, little brother.
And if he ever learned
to control it,
it would be
very bad for us.
So you can see! I have no
choice! He must die. Now.
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU]
No. Wait... You can't...
[RADITZ thinking]
You are the first Saiyan
to ever damage me
like this, my nephew.
You are a true warrior who
is worthy of being a Saiyan.
[RADITZ thinking] And so,
I will give you a death
that is also
worthy of a Saiyan.
[RADITZ screams]
Why, you wretch!
I should have killed you!
[RADITZ grunts]
[GOKU] Piccolo!
Your attack! Let's go!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
Goku, sometimes
you amaze even me!
Now, hold tight!
This will take some time...
And don't listen to
anything he says!
[RADITZ yells and grunts]
See? It never pays to
tell a lie, now, does it?
You little scoundrel!
[RADITZ grunts]
[GOKU] Piccolo!
Hurry up!
I can't hold him
much longer!
[RADITZ thinking] How could
that little brat's attack
weaken me so much?
Kakarot!
You're a fool!
How do you expect
to dodge that beam
and hold me at
the same time?
Heh, heh. You're right,
I can't. We'll both go!
What?
That's insane!
You'll be killed!
Is that what you want?
[GOKU] If it's the only
way for me to beat you!
Hold on, Goku!
I'm almost ready!
So you're going to
sacrifice yourself...
Goku, how very noble of you.
And how convenient for me.
[PICCOLO thinking] Then again,
even if I do kill you,
it's only a matter of time
before your friends
wish you back with the
Dragon Balls... Too bad.
[RADITZ and GOKU grunt]
No you don't!
No way!
[grunting continues]
[GOKU]
Piccolo, my ribs are broken!
Ah! Hurry!
[PICCOLO] I'm almost
there, Goku! Hang on!
[beeping]
[RADITZ] 1440!
No! If that hits,
we're finished!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Hey! Kakarot! Look!
If you don't let me go, right
now, we're both going to die!
What's wrong? You seem a
little scared, brother!
You're a Saiyan!
Don't sacrifice yourself
for these Earth dogs!
[GOKU] It's nice to know that
you're so worried about me!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] Prepare
yourself, Goku! It's time!
[RADITZ grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[PICCOLO] Special
Beam Cannon... Fire!
Kakarot!
[PICCOLO yells]
[RADITZ screams]
Aaaaahhhh!
Curse... you!
[PICCOLO breathes heavily]
Kakarot... How could he?
It makes no sense!
The fool...
Now we're both dead...
No. You die alone.
Goku won't be
gone for long.
I'm guessing his
friends will see to it
he's back
within the week!
What? That's impossible!
Tell me... How?
Heh. Gladly! On this
planet we have something
that we call
the Dragon Balls.
When all seven balls
are gathered together,
they have the power
to grant any wish.
And that includes bringing
the dead back to life.
So you see...
It's Goku who will
have the last laugh.
[RADITZ chuckles and groans]
No... I'm afraid you're
wrong, green man...
This device on my face...
It's... It's also
a transmitter...
My Saiyan comrades
heard every single word.
[PICCOLO] Huh?
[RADITZ]
The two of them...
Now they'll come...
I know they will.
They will...
I know they will...
And once they arrive you'll
be powerless to stop them.
There's nothing
you can do...
They'll seek out
these Dragon Balls.
And they'll destroy
everything in their path!
[RADITZ chuckles and groans]
You and every living
thing on this planet
will be wiped out.
They'll destroy you all.
[GOKU] When...
When will they come?
How long will it take
them to get here?
One year. And the
funny thing is...
[RADITZ chuckles]
They're much
stronger than me.
Stronger?
One year?
Oh, no.
So enjoy this little
victory of yours today.
It means...
It means nothing...
You're as good as dead...
[RADITZ chuckles and groans]
[RADITZ] I only hope I'm back
in time to see it happen...
Don't look so upset...
We can't all have
the last laugh.
[RADITZ laughs]
[PICCOLO yells]
[CHICHI hums]
[CHICHI thinking] Hm.
Goku should've been home by now.
I guess he lost
track of time,
seeing all his old
friends again...
Still, I wish
he'd hurry.
It's not good
for Gohan
to be away from his
studies this long...
Oh well, I suppose it's
all right this time.
Gohan works
so hard.
He deserves to have a little
fun once in a while...
Come to think of it,
so do I...
[whirring]
Huh?
[OX KING]
ChiChi! Gohan!
Ahh!
Hey Dad!
[OX KING] Hey darling!
[OX KING chuckles]
I thought I'd come to
see how you were doing.
So... Where's
my grandson?
Gohan! I have
something for you!
[OX KING grunts]
Ha, ha, ha! Oh, dad!
Okay. I think this
is the place...
[ROSHI] Mm-hm.
[BULMA] They should be right
down there somewhere...
[PICCOLO]
Thanks for the warning...
We'll deal with
your Saiyan friends
just like we
dealt with you.
Goku... It's over.
He's gone.
[KRILLIN]
Hey! Look!
There they are!
[BULMA] Oh, no...
Only one of them's standing.
Who? Who is it?
Piccolo?
Oh no...
This doesn't look good.
[NARRATOR] Even as Goku's
friends rush to his side,
little could they know
that far away,
in a distant corner
of the galaxy,
the events on Earth are being
followed with great interest.
Raditz stinks.
[VEGETA]
He's a complete disgrace...
How could he let himself
be beaten by men
with such low
fighting power?
I don't know.
Maybe we should go teach
those Earthings a lesson.
A waste of time...
Then again,
I am curious...
Oh. Are you thinking
about what Raditz said?
[VEGETA laughs]
Exactly. Those Dragon
Balls caught my interest.
Just think about the
possibilities, Nappa.
If we can get our hands on
those seven Dragon Balls,
then we can wish for
anything that we want.
Anything at all.
Wouldn't you say that's
worth making a little trip?
You kiddin'?
Yeah! Let's go!
Ha, ha, ha , ha, ha!
[KRILLIN] You're going
to make it, Goku!
You can pull through!
No, Krillin.
He can!
Can't you, Goku?
Just tell him!
Say something!
Well, Gohan's
still unconscious.
But otherwise,
I think he's okay.
--[GOKU grunts]
--Eh?
That's good...
Goku...
ChiChi'd kill me
if he got hurt.
Goku...
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU]
K-Krillin...
Please take care
of G-Gohan for me...
Yeah, sure, buddy.
But! It's not gonna
come to that, okay?
You're gonna
make it!
And that's all
there is to it!
Krillin...
No. Not this time, friend.
This time I can't.
I'll wish you
back, Goku.
We already have
three Dragon Balls.
I'll see you... soon...
No...
Goku?
Goku!
[KRILLIN]
[squeaking]
[VEGETA] Once we've forced
Kakarot's friends
to tell us how to find
the Dragon Balls,
we'll eliminate them...
Along with anyone else who
tries to stand in our way...
And then, we can wish
Raditz back to life.
No. That would
be a wasted wish.
Raditz was a weakling
and a fool..
Any Saiyan who could
be defeated so easily
doesn't deserve
to live.
[NAPPA grunts]
[VEGETA]
Actually, Nappa,
I have something far
more grand in mind.
Now tell me, how does the idea
of eternal life sound to you?
What? Living forever?
That sounds great.
Yeah, and if
we can't die,
that means no one'll ever
be able to defeat us...
So what the heck would
we need Raditz for?
Yes, 'what for', indeed?
We'll be the greatest
fighters in the universe.
And we will ascend
to our rightful place
among the Saiyan
warriors of legend!
Do you mean...
[VEGETA]
That's right, Nappa.
That's exactly
what I mean.
We will become
Super Saiyans!
[NAPPA] Now I definitely
like the sound of that!
[KRILLIN sobs]
[KRILLIN] No! Goku!
You can't die! You can't!
[ROSHI]
He's gone.
No, this...
This can't be happening.
I don't believe it.
[ROSHI] Look!
He's disappearing!
What in the world?
I know...
It was Kami.
[KRILLIN] Kami?
The guardian of the Earth.
I think you both know him.
Yes. This is his work...
No doubt Kami has some 'special
purpose' in mind for Goku...
Do you think so?
[NARRATOR] Although Goku has
left the world of the living,
it seems
thanks to Kami,
a bold new adventure awaits
him in the world beyond!
But as Goku begins his
incredible journey
into the unknown,
the friends he leaves behind
must find a way to carry on!
For the time being...
The Earth is without
its greatest champion
and a terrible new
threat is on its way!
In one year, two even
more powerful Saiyans
will land on Earth...
Who will be there
to stop them?
The countdown begins...
Next time on
Dragon Ball Z!