[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
Along with the discovery
of one of the Dragon Balls
within a Namekian tomb,
Gohan successfully
pulled another
from the depths of
a flesh-eating swamp.
Gohan!
Are you okay?
Look what I got!
[NARRATOR] And although our
friends have pulled themselves
out of plenty of dangerous
situations before,
the worst may still
lie ahead of them!
You're fully healed now.
You may open your eyes.
Unfortunately,
we weren't successful
in reconstructing
your tail.
[VEGETA] No matter.
I don't need it.
[NARRATOR] It seems the Prince
is back and ready for battle.
But are Goku and
the gang ready
for the
rebirth of Vegeta?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball Z!
Come on, guys! Just turn
up the heat and let's go.
But we can't
hurry. Sorry.
Yeah, if we used
any more energy
we'd burn straight
through the cavern floor
and then it'd
collapse beneath us.
Okay, okay, just
get on with it!
I don't know how much
more of this I can take!
I mean seriously, this
can't be good for my skin.
It's feeling all
stiff and cold
and not at all like it's usual
delicate self. Oh my gosh.
What does frost bite
feel like anyway?
Can your whole face
get frost bitten?
Do you know? Huh?
[BULMA] Hey,
where'd Zaacro go?
Good, Gohan.
We're almost finished.
[KRILLIN humming]
Ha-ha!
[KRILLIN laughing]
All right...
The sixth one!
One more to go.
[ALL] Yay! Yay!
[ALL laughing]
[distant rumbling]
[BULMA] I thought you guys
said you were extra careful
so this
wouldn't happen!
We were, but you distracted
us with skin care talk!
[ALL screaming]
[sinister laughing]
[screaming]
[ALL shouting]
[GOHAN whimpering]
[BULMA] This is not happening!
This is not happening!
[GOHAN yells]
[shouting]
[BULMA squeals]
[BULMA] If you guys have
anything planned to save us,
now might be
a good time!
[GOHAN] I think
we're in trouble!
[ALL screaming]
[BULMA]
Go left, go left, go left!
Right.
[KRILLIN] Hyaah!
[GOHAN and KRILLIN shout]
Heh. This is great.
You ain't
seen nothin' yet.
[ALL sigh]
That was fun.
Let's do it again!
[BULMA] Huh?
[BULMA] Aah! I don't want
to ride this anymore!
[GOHAN and KRILLIN screaming]
[DR. ROOSTER] Care to tell
me what happened, Vegeta,
or is the wound to your ego
still too raw to be examined?
Judging by these
stress fractures
in your protective armor,
you must have received
quite a beating, and
that's putting it lightly.
I hope you're not entertaining
ideas of revenge.
I might not be here to put
you back together next time.
[VEGETA] Is Frieza here?
I need to see him.
He left. I don't
know where he is.
I hope you're not lying
to me. I'm in no mood.
Perhaps Cui can
help you find him.
I saw him on his way to
the training center earlier.
You could catch him there
before he leaves, if you hurry.
Ha, ha, ha. I have no
use for that coward.
If you see Frieza, tell
him I'm looking for him.
But, Vegeta... Wait!
[DR. ROOSTER]
Vegeta... Vegeta!
Sir, you're leaving
your scouter behind!
[VEGETA] Keep it. It's yours.
I have no use for it.
[GOKU grunting]
[grunting continues]
Taah!
[GOKU yelling]
I guess I overdid
it there a little.
I should learn to
start out smaller.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunting]
Huh?
[GOKU laughing]
At least my
nose still works.
I've always heard
you should stop
and take the time
to smell the flowers.
[ALL yelling]
[whimpering]
C'mon, Krillin, stop this
ride, I wanna get off!
Gohan...
Look at the ceiling.
What? Huh?
I hope you're not thinking
what I think you're thinking...
[BULMA screams]
[BOTH] Haah!
[ALL screaming]
Hey, you guys, does that
look like an exit to you?
'Cause it sure
does to me!
You're right!
[ALL laughing]
[squealing]
[BULMA screaming]
[crashing]
[KRILLIN]
That was some exit.
[BULMA sighs]
It seems we're
getting close.
[GOHAN]
Awesome.
It's not that
I doubt you,
but you sure we're going in
the right direction, Bulma?
Yes!
All right, all right.
I believe you.
[GOHAN laughing]
[VOICE] Yes.
[sinister laughing]
Is it time?
Yes.
[BULMA]
Good news, guys.
Dragon Ball
straight ahead!
[KRILLIN] Wait a minute...
I've been here before.
[BULMA]
Earth to Krillin!
You coming or what?
[GOHAN laughing]
[BULMA] According
to the Radar,
the Dragon Ball should be
somewhere near that lake.
[BULMA] It looks to be in that
stone building over there.
[BULMA] Yep. I'm
sure it's in there.
I don't doubt it,
but my question is,
are you sure it's
safe to go in there?
Don't worry, Krillin.
If you don't want to go,
I can get the
Dragon Ball for you.
So, Krillin,
don't tell me
you're just gonna
sit around scared
and let a little boy
do your job for you.
I'm not sitting,
I'm standing.
[BULMA] Well, whatever. Stand
around scared for all I care,
but Gohan and I are
going in there, right?
Right.
[KRILLIN]
But, Bulma--
I don't want to
hear it, Krillin!
We only need one
more Dragon Ball
then we can wish
all of our friends back.
I'm not gonna let you
stand in the way
of us accomplishing
that, understand?
Uh... Uh-huh.
Okay, then. Let's go get
this thing over with.
I'm in desperate need
of some beauty sleep.
Mm-hmm.
Understand?
[BOTH]
Mm-hmm.
I just hope my
frostbitten face
doesn't scare away
Yamcha when I see him.
So, will it? And
I want an honest answer,
no patronizing, please.
You look
radiant, Bulma.
[GOHAN] Um...
[thinking] Only one
more Dragon Ball,
and I'll finally be
able to see Piccolo again!
[GOHAN grunting]
Krillin!
[GOHAN] Bulma!
Somebody help me!
[GOHAN grunting]
Eh? What's happening?
Would you quit
clowning around?
We don't have
time to play!
But I'm not...
Something's got a hold of
me, and I can't get free!
[KRILLIN] Gohan!
[BULMA screaming]
[RAITI and ZAACRO laughing]
Ah! I've found him.
[CHICHI] Goodness, what
is Goku doing out here
in the middle
of nowhere?
[ROSHI] Hm? I'll tell
you what he's doing.
[ROSHI] What he always does:
taking on too much too soon.
[thinking] There's
nothing I want more
than to
return to Earth
and pay a little
visit to Kakarot.
But first, to planet Namek.
I need to pick something up.
[SOLDIER] Well, Vegeta,
I hear you took quite a
beating recently.
[laughing]
You couldn't even take
over one measly planet.
And if all the
rumors are true,
which I'm sure
they are,
you couldn't beat a
third-class Saiyan.
Drop it, Cui.
I don't have time
to waste gossiping
with half-wits
like you.
Just a minute.
The word is that Frieza
isn't too happy with you
and your
attitude, Vegeta.
[VEGETA laughing]
[VEGETA] Just let Frieza try
to do something about it.
[VEGETA] Now, get
your hand off me.
[CUI]
Your mouth is big,
but I think you're biting
off more than you can chew.
You don't know what
you're up against, Vegeta.
Nobody has survived
a fight with Frieza.
You just don't seem
to get it, do you?
Let me put
it plainly:
Frieza is utterly
indestructible.
Enough! Now tell me where
Frieza has run off to hide!
The planet Namek.
[thinking] What?!
But how could he know?
If I don't beat him
to the Dragon Balls,
then I'll never be
able to defeat him!
Why don't you do the smart
thing and just give up?
Because you will never
get those Dragon Balls.
Believe me, Vegeta.
Frieza will most
certainly find them first,
and when he does, will
destroy the planet Namek.
[VEGETA] I can't give up!
[CUI] Wait! Vegeta!
Vegeta?
[VEGETA] Wait...
On second thought, I think
I'll be needing this, Doctor.
[CUI] Vegeta!
All right, Frieza!
I'm coming for you!
You two better let
me go this instant.
See my friend over there?
He knows karate!
[RAITI and ZAACRO laughing]
[ZAACRO] It's unfortunate,
but playtime is over.
Playtime?
[RAITI] Time to get
down to business.
[BOTH growling]
[BULMA yelling]
Hey! I recognize
you two guys!
It was you in the hieroglyphics
I found in the cave.
Correct.
Give the
boy a prize.
[rumbling]
Okay, according
to the Radar...
Three left!
[thinking]
This can't be real...
It's all an
illusion!
[GOHAN screaming]
[MONSTERS growling]
[roaring]
[GOHAN yelling]
[RAITI]
Go ahead, cueball.
Aren't you gonna save
your little friend?
[ZAACRO] But be warned.
Those creatures
are meat eaters.
Gohan! Bulma!
[GOHAN screaming]
[RAITI laughing]
[NARRATOR] Is this
really planet Namek?
What could have changed
this beautiful place
into such a
nightmarish land?
Vegeta, speeding towards the
planet searching for Frieza,
will find much more
than he bargained for
when he reaches
the surface.
And what
about Goku?
Will he come to in time to
help straighten out this mess?
For the answers to all
of your questions,
tune in to the next
exciting adventure
on Dragon Ball Z!
[RAITI and ZAACRO laugh]