[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta unleashed
his terror
upon an unsuspecting
Namekian village,
and his conquest has brought
him one step closer
to achieving his
ultimate goal.
By taking one of
the Dragon Balls
and hiding it in
the watery depths,
Vegeta ensured that
Frieza and his men
would not be able to
gather all seven.
Now, there is only one
Dragon Ball left to find,
and then Vegeta can
focus on stealing
the five already in
Frieza's possession.
Meanwhile, as events
unfolded on Namek,
Goku raced through space
to meet these deadly foes.
But his intensive
training session
was unexpectedly
interrupted!
[KING KAI]
Goku, can you hear me?
[NARRATOR] It was King Kai!
With exciting news...
You gotta be kidding me!
Everyone made it?
They all reached you together?
That's great, King Kai!
[KING KAI chuckles]
You guessed it!
They're here, and they
want me to train them
even harder than
I trained you!
[NARRATOR] The adventure
continues... Today!
[YAMCHA] King Kai,
can I say hello to him?
Of course. Just rest your hand
on my shoulder and speak.
Hey, Goku,
guess who?
Hey! Yamcha! I'm glad
to hear you made it okay!
Yeah. The trip down Snake
Way wasn't all that bad.
It's this increased
gravity here
that's gonna be hard
to get used to.
[GOKU] Heh! Believe me,
I know what you mean.
I've been trying to
do some training
under heavy
gravity myself.
I'm on my
way to meet
Bulma, Krillin, and
Gohan on Planet Namek.
And unless I get a lot stronger
in the next five days,
we're gonna be in
serious trouble.
Uh? Why's that?
What's wrong, Goku?
Well, while I was
in the hospital,
Krillin, Bulma, and
Gohan decided to go
to Planet Namek
without me
so they could start
looking for the Dragon Balls.
But, when they
got there,
they found out that
Vegeta was there, too,
trying to do
the same thing!
--[YAMCHA] Oh, no!
--[KING KAI screams]
What happened? Did
Vegeta try to attack them?!
[TIEN] Huh?
No... Not yet. They've
managed to avoid him so far.
I don't think he
knows they're there.
But, it gets worse.
It looks like there's another
force on the planet.
I don't know
who they are,
but they've been searching
for the Dragon Balls, too.
I guess they're
not Saiyans,
even though Bulma says they
wear the same uniforms.
But it sounds like
they're some bad guys.
And, if that
wasn't bad enough,
their leader is supposed to be
even more powerful than Vegeta!
[BOTH] No way!
What's up?
What's going on there?
There's... There's a...
A fighter...
Even stronger than
Vegeta on Namek...
You... didn't happen to
catch his name, did you?
Is it Frieza?
[GOKU] Sorry, I don't know.
Bulma didn't say.
[KING KAI whimpering]
Well, Goku, I'd better take
a look, just to be sure.
That's great.
Thanks, King Kai.
[KING KAI] Let's see...
I think I get the best
signals from Namek over here.
Yamcha, what does
all this mean?
[KING KAI grunts]
I can sense an enormous
power level already!
Now if I can just see
where it's coming from...
Noooo!
It's Friezaaaa!
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU] Hey! What's wrong?
Did you see who it is?
Goku, listen to me!
This is the strongest
and fiercest opponent
you could ever face!
There's no way
you're ready for him!
But... What do you
mean, King Kai?
[KING KAI] I'm not just saying
this for your sake, Goku,
but for all
people everywhere!
You can't
anger Frieza!
If you do, his wrath
will follow us
to the ends of
the universe!
I'm ordering you not to
go anywhere near him!
Now, you promise me!
Promise you won't attempt
to face Frieza at any cost!
You can't win.
All you'd do is provoke him!
It would be just like hitting
a beehive with a stick!
The best thing you can do is
stay away from him altogether.
But, what about
the Dragon Balls?
I at least
have to try.
No! You have to
promise me! Right now!
Come on...
Absolutely nooooot!
Hey. Don't
listen to him.
You just get those Dragon Balls
and wish us back to life.
Piccolo!
[PICCOLO] In the meantime,
we'll do some training
with King Kai
to get ready.
Yeah!
Between you, me,
Gohan, and Krillin,
we should be able
to handle this guy.
[KING KAI grunts]
No! You don't have any idea
what you're talking about!
[PICCOLO] There's no time
to waste. Start training us.
[KING KAI] No way! Not if
you're going to fight Frieza!
Promise you won't! That's
the only way I'll teach you!
All right.
I hope you mean that.
I'm trusting you.
And all of
you, too!
[ALL] Mm-hmm.
[thinking] Heh, heh, heh.
He's crazy if he thinks
I'm gonna stick
to that promise.
[thinking] I've got to train
hard, just like Goku.
His strength increased
so much it was amazing.
For us to face
this Frieza,
we'll all have to
be at our best.
Hmph.
Good. Now, let's
get started.
[thinking] I've been waiting
for this training forever.
[thinking]
Show me what you've got.
[KING KAI] Are you sure
you're ready for this?
[YAMCHA] Hmm.
Fine, in that case...
Then your first challenge
is to make me laugh!
You don't make me laugh,
I don't train you! Got it?
[ALL gasp]
Okay, even if don't
fight this Frieza,
he didn't say I
couldn't keep training!
Alright! Let's see what I can
do under thirty-times gravity!
Hey, so if we keep on
flying at this speed,
how long will it
take us to get there?
Well... I'd guess
about five more hours.
[KRILLIN sighs]
Bah! I should've
been able to sense
some more of these
Nameks by now!
Where are they?
There must be a village
around here somewhere!
[thinking] Wait a second.
I do sense something.
It's faint, but there's
two of them moving.
And they're not
with Frieza.
Interesting. Let's see
where they're headed.
[NARRATOR] And so, the
great joke contest began.
[KING KAI laughing]
[NARRATOR] Yamcha and
Chiaotzu proved themselves
to be quite
the comedians.
However, Tien and
Piccolo are having
a much more difficult time
getting King Kai to laugh.
[PICCOLO scoffs]
I... quit.
[CHIAOTZU] C'mon, Tien.
You can't give up.
Use this one.
[whispering]
[KING KAI] Huuuh...?
I don't know. Doesn't
sound very funny to me.
It'll work!
Trust me, that joke's
right up his alley!
All right.
I'm ready.
Go Tien!
Make him laugh!
Let's do it.
Your move.
[BOTH whimper]
Here goes.
Now! You can tune...
What was next?
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH yell]
You can tune...
Ohh...?
Ehh...
Piano! A piano!
[thinking] I've never
felt pressure like this.
I must focus. Focus.
Aww... Is that it?
[TIEN growls]
No!
Oh, my... He's taking
this seriously.
[BOTH whimpering]
You can tune a piano,
but you can't tuna fish!
[KING KAI screaming]
[TIEN] Did you catch all
of that?! Huh, King Kai?!
I said you can tune a piano,
but you can't tuna fiiiiish!
[KING KAI sighing]
[TIEN panting]
[KING KAI whimpering]
[screams]
[KING KAI laughing hysterically]
All right!
There you go,
Tien, old buddy!
Yay, yay, yay!
[CHIAOTZU] See, Tien?
I told you you can be funny!
Bah! Pathetic.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN] Dende, stop!
It's Vegeta!
He must have sensed us!
He's heading this
way! And fast!
He'll be here
any second!
C'mon! Hurry! We've
gotta get out of sight!
[DENDE whimpering]
Huh?
[DENDE whimpers]
Huh?!
Huh? Uh...
Uh... What's going on?
Why'd he take off like that?
Huh?!
There's another
big power level...
Vegeta must
be after him!
It's Zarbon! I'm sure of it!
And he's alone. Perfect.
Without Frieza to protect
him, he'll be easy prey!
[GOKU grunting]
[grunting continues]
[GOKU pants]
No good...
It's still too easy.
I'll have to turn it up
to 50-times gravity!
[panting continues]
[KING KAI] Alright, it's time
to begin our training.
At first it may seem
tough... For wimps!
[KING KAI giggles]
[laughing hysterically]
I was just kidding!
[laughing continues]
[KING KAI] Tough crowd! And
they know I won't train anyone
without a
sense of humor!
[ALL gasp]
[CHIAOTZU &amp; YAMCHA laugh]
[ALL laughing]
That's more like it. You're
a regular bunch of hyenas!
[KING KAI laughs]
[laughing]
Now, it's time for
training to begin.
Jeez... Hey,
Bubbles! You're up!
[ALL] Huh?
[BUBBLES chatters]
[ALL gasp]
Your first
training exercise
will be to try
to catch Bubbles.
Uh... You're kidding me!
That's it?
Kay, piece of cake!
You think so?
I'll have you know,
it took Goku almost
three weeks to do it.
[YAMCHA squeals]
Goku?!
[thinking] Three weeks
to catch a monkey.
Question!
Uh, yes?
So if we catch the monkey,
does that mean we're ready
to start the real
training with you?
Not quite. If you
can handle Bubbles,
we'll see how you
fare against Gregory.
And then I'll know if you're
ready for my teaching.
How's that sound?
[ALL] Mm-hmm.
Good.
[PICCOLO] Hmph.
Run like the
wind, Bubbles!
[BUBBLES chatters]
[ALL grunting]
[YAMCHA] This is hard!
Wait up!
Good luck boys!
[KING KAI] You'll need it...
Hmm?
Huh?!
[KING KAI screams]
What the--!
[KING KAI growling]
So, what
do you say
we get on to the real
training. No more games.
Not so fast!
You haven't earned the
right to train with me yet!
[TIEN &amp; YAMCHA panting]
[PICCOLO growls]
Fine! Just
forget it then!
I don't have time for this
monkey business anyway.
[muffled giggling]
[PICCOLO] Hmm...?
Ah!
[muffled giggling]
Oh, that's
a good one!
Really... A riot...
Monkey Business...
[KING KAI laughing hysterically]
[KING KAI]
Congratulations, Piccolo!
You passed the laugh test!
I'll train you now.
[laughing continues]
[KING KAI] Oh, come on
guys! It was funny!
Just the way he said it!
"Monkey business!"
[KING KAI giggles]
[KING KAI] No?
Still nothing?
Oh well, I can tell
you one thing:
You guys have a lot to learn
learn about comedy! Sheesh...
Blast! I could
kill that old Namek
for destroying
our scouters.
Too bad he's
already dead.
Vegeta!
So. We finally meet again,
Zarbon. What a surprise.
I've already disposed of
that useless Dodoria.
Now I plan to do
the same thing to you.
What?! There's no way you
beat Dodoria by yourself!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Whatever
you say, Zarbon...
I say you're lying!
It's easy
enough to prove.
If you don't believe me, why
don't you try me for yourself?
You're a fool.
You should know better
than to disobey Frieza.
Yes, so I've heard.
But unlike you,
I've never been suited to the
life of a mindless follower.
I'm through
taking orders.
I'm through cowering
before Frieza like a dog.
And I intend to see
him grovel at my feet,
as soon as I've
made my wish!
You mean with the
Dragon Balls.
The winds of change
are blowing, Zarbon.
Soon, the power of
immortality will be mine!
And with it, I will
rule this galaxy forever!
[ZARBON] You're dreaming! Frieza
already has five Dragon Balls.
It won't take us long
to find the rest.
[VEGETA] Please. You're
blind without your scouters.
That's a liability
I don't share.
My powers have
improved in more ways
than you could
ever imagine.
[ZARBON chuckles]
So you've learned some
new tricks, then?
It doesn't
change a thing.
What makes you think
your abilities
even hold a candle
to Frieza's?
I'd say you already know
the answer to that question!
Dodoria did too!
And before he died,
he told me everything!
Frieza fears
the Saiyans!
Which means,
he's afraid of me!
Don't flatter yourself.
What Frieza feared was
the entire Saiyan race
rising up
against him.
All alone, you're
no threat to anyone.
Well.
We'll see.
[ZARBON grunting]
[VEGETA chuckling,
ZARBON grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[ZARBON shouts]
[ZARBON grunts]
[ZARBON]
Haaaah!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Rraaahh!
[ZARBON gasps]
You surprise
me, Vegeta.
Whoa... Those power
levels are incredible!
I guess that's where Vegeta
ran off to in such a hurry.
Yeah, that's
him all right.
He must be fighting one of
Frieza's goons or something.
Well, good.
I say let 'em fight.
Maybe we'll get lucky and
they'll take each other out.
'Cause if either
one finds us...
[DENDE whimpering]
[KRILLIN] Hey!
Hang on tight, kid!
We gotta move!
If we turn up the speed,
we might be able to get
to the Eldest Namek
while they're
still fighting!
Let's hope
they're too busy
beating each other
up to notice!
[ZARBON grunting]
[VEGETA laughing]
[ZARBON gasps]
[VEGETA]
Hyah!
[ZARBON grunting]
[VEGETA laughing]
[VEGETA] Well, I think I
proved my point, Zarbon!
[ZARBON whimpering]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[whimpering becomes chuckling]
Hmm...?
[ZARBON laughing]
[ZARBON]
Well, I have to admit...
You do impress me, Vegeta.
Your fighting skills
have come a long way
since the last time we met,
but not quite far enough!
[ZARBON chuckling]
[NARRATOR] Even with
all of his might,
it seems
Vegeta's attacks
have had little effect
on the terrifying Zarbon.
Has the Saiyan prince
finally met his match?
Find out in the next explosive
episode of Dragon Ball Z!