[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu continued
his random destruction
of the cities of the Earth.
With no greater motive than
his own childish amusement,
Buu had already
annihilated two thirds
of the planet's population.
And still counting!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile,
Goku arrived at the
Check-in Station.
Goku, I'm surprised at you.
You're not going to
cut in line, are you?
I sure am! Don't tell!
You crack me up!
So long!
[NARRATOR] Inside, a grumpy
King Yemma confirmed
that Gohan had not
checked in! He was alive!
Really? Woo, hoo! Yay, yay!
He's not dead! Awesome!
[laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Using Instant Transmission,
Goku was able to
find the special sanctuary
where Supreme Kai was
overseeing Gohan's training
with the Z Sword!
[NARRATOR] It was a
hair-raising arrival for Goku,
but now that father
and son have reunited,
let the training begin!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fusion! Ha!
[PICCOLO]
Again!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fu-sion! Ha!
You're not synchronized!
You've got to stay focused!
All right, take a breather.
Listen. It's not
just body movement.
Before you become one,
you have to be one.
You've got to think
the same thoughts,
breathe in the same rhythm!
How can I breathe when
he's cuttin' silent ones?
Look who's talking!
Your breath smells like death!
It does not!
Does too!
[PICCOLO]
Errrgh! Enough!
What do you think you're doing?!
Get a hold of yourselves!
Can't you two sense what's
going on below us right now?
Innocent people
are being killed
and you're acting like this!
[TRUNKS grumbles]
[sighs]
Errm!
All right! Are we ready?
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Yes...
[PICCOLO]
Then let's see it then!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fusion! Ha!
[PICCOLO]
Much better! Again!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fusion! Ha!
[PICCOLO]
Again!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fusion! Ha!
[ANDROID 18]
Fusion! Uhh!
I tell ya! It's enough to
drive someone crazy, isn't it?
[ANDROID 18] I even
dreamed about it last night.
Puar was trying to
fuse with the Ox-King!
[BULMA]
Ooh! How awful!
Hey!
What? You think you're
about to win, don't you?
Well, forget it!
[KRILLIN] Let's see. Uh,
which one do I want? Uh...
[KRILLIN] Hmm...
It's so hard to know.
[ROSHI] Hm?
How strange!
Fusing together!
It's hard to imagine
those two as one boy.
[ROSHI] I wonder if boys
can fuse with girls.
[BULMA] Good questions.
Aaah!
[ROSHI laughs]
Why, thank you!
That's just the card
I wanted you to pick!
Heh, heh!
Haaa...!
[grunting]
Huaaah!
[GOKU]
Wow! Cool!
Haaa!
[GOKU]
Yeah! Nice!
Looking good, Gohan!
I'm impressed!
[chuckles]
[GOKU] I can't believe
that you've mastered it
like that in one day!
That's incredible, son!
[SUPREME KAI] Yes! Handling
the Z Sword in this fashion
is unprecedented.
You should be
very proud of yourself!
[chuckles nervously]
Gohan! Whatd'ya say we
put that baby to the test
and see how sharp it is?
Sure!
[GOKU] Great.
I'll toss. You slice.
Sounds good to me, Dad!
Let's see now. Hmm...
Yeah! Why not?
Uhuhhh, aah!
[GOKU] Let's start out
with this small one.
[GOHAN] Right, Dad.
Ready when you are.
[SUPREME KAI]
That's a small one?
'Kay! Coming atcha!
I hope this doesn't
over-stress the blade!
Nah! It'll handle it
like a champion!
Just watch and see!
After all,
this is the Z Sword!
[GOKU]
All right! Batter up!
[grunts]
[GOHAN]
Hu-aah!
[gasps]
[laughs]
My! That was superb, Gohan!
Thank you!
[KIBITO]
Yes! Amazing! Truly!
[laughs]
I think you're ready
for a big one, son!
[SUPREME KAI]
Just a minute!
[GOKU]
Uh?
How about more density
and a little less mass?
Here, Goku. Catch.
Eee!
Whoa! What's this?
That is the hardest known
metal in the Universe.
It's called Katchin.
Oh, Katchin?
[SUPREME KAI] Yes. This will
be a much better test.
[GOKU]
You're not kidding!
Hey. Gohan. Ready?
[GOHAN]
Let her fly, Dad!
All right! Here it comes!
[GOKU yells]
[GOHAN yells]
[yells]
Eee!
Uh!
Huh? Oh, no!
Now it's the Z Dagger!
[chuckles nervously]
Please! No! Tell me
it's not true, Kibito!
It's true!
It snapped in two!
Uh, oh! Wow!
I-I guess it's probably
called the "hardest metal
in the universe"
for a reason, isn't it.
But he who masters the sword
is supposed to have
the greatest power
in the Universe!
Wield the sword and you can
not be rivaled! It's legend!
Huh! I guess they must have
exaggerated a little bit!
Hey, guys! Look!
There is definitely a
bright side to all of this.
The sword training has made me
a lot stronger and faster.
See! Maybe the legend
means that the person
who is able to master
the handling of the Z Sword
attains the greatest
power in the Universe!
Hey, whatd'ya think?
Yes! It's possible!
Your power has definitely
increased from handling it!
And if you're
stronger at this level,
that means you'll be much
stronger as a Super Saiyan!
Mm! Mmm!
Yes! Sure! That must be it!
Gohan doesn't need the sword,
he's already gained the power!
Yeah but, does Gohan's power
surpass Majin Buu's?
I'm not so sure.
[gasps]
What are you saying, Goku?
That we don't have a chance?
[MALE VOICE]
Quiet!
[BOTH shriek]
[MAN chuckles]
Ahh! Much better!
[chuckles]
Uh, sir. We were in
the middle of training.
[MAN]
You call that training?
[laughs]
[SUPREME KAI] Who are you?
How did you get here?
Who me?
Check out the
hair-style, youngster.
And the ear-loops! Yes! Yes!
Oh, and the dashing looks!
I'm just an
older version of you!
Fifteen generations
to be precise! I'm Kai!
What?! Fifteen...
generations ago?
What? There're two
Supreme Kai's?
[GOHAN]
Mm-mmm!
[indistinct chatter]
[ATTENDANT 1]
Please remain calm!
King Yemma is working
as fast as he can!
Uhh! Excuse me, King Yemma?
What now?
Please, sir. We've been
working around the clock.
Can we please
just take a break?
Take a break?!
Uhh! We're starving,
our armpits stink,
and our feet ache!
We just want to take a shower
and get something to eat!
[ATTENDANT 1] My horns
are throbbing, King Yemma!
We just need a little rest!
A little rest
would do us all good!
But while I'm in charge,
we get the job done first!
[BOTH sigh]
Try to remember the days
when there weren't any souls.
And the two of you
stood around doing nothing!
While still getting paid!
[BOTH whimper]
[ATTENDANT 3]
King Yemma! More arrivals!
How many?
[ATTENDANT 3]
They're all from Earth, sir.
We estimate one million
five hundred thousand!
One million?!
[ATTENDANT 3]
And a half, sir. Yes.
[YEMMA grunts]
This is ridiculous!
Where's Goku when you need him?
You're how many years old?
Fifteen generations?
Remarkable, aye?
[coughs wheezingly]
Well then. Now. Yes.
I'm sure you're wondering how
I'm still alive. So listen!
There was a terrible villain
who lived way back then.
Well, not as
terrible as Majin Buu,
but still pretty bad.
The only thing he
feared was that
I would use my
awesome powers to stop him
and his evil ways.
So he tricked me.
He sealed me away
inside the Z Sword!
From whence I came.
[SUPREME KAI] You mean
you were trapped inside
the Z Sword all this time?
[OLD KAI] Mm, hmm! I sure was!
Now I've got a cramp!
I don't think this guy looks
as strong as he says, do you?
Not really.
Hey! Let's put him to the test!
What? Dad? I don't know if...
[GOKU]
Sshhh! Watch!
Ya!
[OLD KAI]
Aah!
[ALL yell]
[SUPREME KAI]
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
Oh my dear ancestor!
[KIBITO] Please! Venerable Sir!
Are you all right?
How dare you?! Babies!
Babies in diapers!
That's what you two are!
Trying an attack like that on
a fearsome presence like me!
Are you cracked?!
Aah!
But sir! That attack
was just child's play!
My little brother
coulda handled that!
All of my enemies feared me!
But not because of
my strength!
My menacing capacities
are what struck terror
into their hearts!
Capacities?
Menacing?
Hmm? What do you mean?
I'm not telling! Nope!
Give me one good reason
why I should! Huh?
Blaaa, naaa!
[GOKU] Well, hmm...
Let me see here...
I got it! My old master
likes girly magazines!
We'll get you some!
Oh, boy! Uhh, Dad?
Goku, please!
How inappropriate!
Hm! I have no need
for such things!
With my omniscient vision,
I can see girls playing
volleyball on the beach!
[laughs]
You call yourself a Kai?!
[GOKU]
Hey, old man!
How 'bout we get you a date
with a real live Earth woman!
Mm! Is she a good kisser?
Yeah! Of course!
[laughs]
[GOKU thinking]
What luck!
This guy's just
like Master Roshi!
Dad? Are you nuts?
How are you going
to find someone
that wants to kiss that guy?
Hey! Don't worry. I can't go
back to Earth, but you can.
This is all too simple.
You can handle it, son.
It might require a
little sacrifice, though.
Can you get Videl to do it?
Dad, I'm not going
to ask my girlfriend
to kiss that old relic!
Okay! Okay! Sheesh!
Who else do we know?
[ROSHI] Well, I haven't heard
any Fusion Ha's in a while.
Piccolo must be
giving them a break.
It feels a little strange
to be playing cards
with the world being destroyed
right beneath us. Hmm!
How weird! I just had an
intense deja-vu, you guys!
Two cards.
Strange! I must've lived
through this before. Yeah!
[chuckles]
Then you know
you're about to lose!
Let's see. Come on! Please...
Yay! I did it! Ha-ha-ha!
Royal Flush!
Read 'em and weep!
[ROSHI, KRILLIN yell]
[BULMA giggles]
[GOKU sighs]
Hm...
Okay, I have someone in mind
but she's not exactly
a spring chicken.
Hm! It doesn't really matter.
As long as
she's a good kisser!
Hey what about Bulma?
She'd do it!
Do you think
she's a good kisser?
What? Why are you asking me?
I don't want any part of this!
Just getting
the details straight!
Now was that with
lipstick or without?
With! Definitely with! Yes!
Either way
would be fine, really.
I think it's worth it if this
guy's powers can help us win!
Bulma will listen
to you Gohan.
One kiss
could save the world!
Dad! Have you looked
at that guy? Come on!
And what if his so called
powers don't help?
Do you know how mad
Bulma would be at me
if she kissed him for nothing?
It's a done deal.
Man, you're good!
So what are these
"capacities" of yours?
[clears throat]
How shall I say this?
Guess I'll put it
in layman's terms.
If I use my powers on a kitty
cat that goes "meow,"
he'll go...
[lion's roar]
Get it?
In other words, an ordinary
cat becomes a lion.
So you see...
Therein lies my talent--
I awaken people's
sleeping powers!
[SUPREME KAI, KIBITO gasp]
Oh, so then... you're not
really that strong yourself.
You fool! I can take a
person far beyond his limits!
Ugh! The bird becomes
an eagle! Get it?!
Yeah, it's just a
little hard to believe.
[chuckles nervously]
[OLD KAI]
Young people!
You! How would you like to
have your sleeping
powers awakened?
Who? Me?
Yeah, you! Get over there!
Okay...
A guy like you with the
power to break the Z Sword--
I can do something with you.
Yes, you have great potential!
Funny though.
I always thought
it would be a Kai
that broke the
Z sword and rescued me.
But you're more of a shoe-shine
boy than a hero, huh?
The Kai's being
rescued by mere mortals.
Things have
sure gone down hill.
Mm! Well, sir,
I've always tried my best.
[OLD KAI]
Keep your chin up, lad!
Keep your chin up!
There.
Stay where you are, son.
Remain perfectly still.
Right.
Now just relax.
Wake up you lazy,
no good powers.
Mmm!
Sleeping all of this time!
How dare you?! Wake up!
[SUPREME KAI gulps]
[OLD KAI moans, grunts]
Uh...
[OLD KAI mumbles nonsensically]
Wake up, you!
Sleeping powers! Wake up now!
Whoo, wooo, wooo!
[GOHAN]
Uh, excuse me.
--[GOHAN] Uh... sir.
--[OLD KAI] Quiet, please!
Be still. This is what
sets the mood.
Sets the mood?
But I thought...
Well, stop thinking. This is
just the opening ceremony.
[nonsensical mumbles continue]
Good grief! Wow! What next?
Excuse me. How long
is this going to take?
Five more hours.
Power raising.
Twenty more after that.
[GOHAN]
Aaah...!
[chuckles]
Well, bye guys. I'm gonna go
take a little nap.
Do your best, Gohan!
Dad! Don't go!
[GOKU] Get me up when your
sleeping powers wake up.
[chants nonsensically]
Well, Kibito this is quite an
unexpected turn of events.
Yes, sir. Very odd.
Why me?
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fusion! Ha!
Fu...sion! Ha!
Good! You've got it!
Your form is nearly perfect.
[BOTH]
Ah-aah!
All right.
Now it's time to see
if you two can actually do it!
Boys. Align your energies.
This is it!
[BOTH]
Right!
[PICCOLO] Remember.
Breathe in the same rhythm.
And when you see each other,
don't think of yourselves
as separate or different.
You're just seeing
another part of yourself.
Okay! Ready?!
[BOTH]
Yes!
[NARRATOR] It seems that Trunks
and Goten are getting closer
to reaching their goal.
But what about Gohan?
Does the mysterious old Kai
really have the power
to bring him
to higher heights?
Gohan seems skeptical!
As Supreme Kai marvels
at his ancient ancestor,
Goku drifts off
into a dreamy sleep,
worlds away from
any cares or concerns.
He'll need his rest...
for the next action packed
episode of Dragon Ball Z!