Hyaah!
[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
two of the elite
Ginyu Force members
launched their attack on Goku.
The tables were turned however
as Burter was no match
for our hero's new power.
[NARRATOR] Upon hearing the news
of his team's
failure from Jeice,
Captain Ginyu decided to take
matters into his own hands and
the pair returned
to the battlefield.
[NARRATOR] A showdown between
two of the strongest fighters
in the universe was
about to take place.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Frieza,
sped toward Guru's house,
with his sights set on
wishing for immortality.
[thinking] I'll be like a God!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[NARRATOR] The Dragon Balls
weren't working for him
and he wanted to know why!
[NARRATOR] As Ginyu
was assessing
Goku's potential power,
Krillin and Gohan were
assigned a mission
to get the
Dragon Balls back,
and Goku formed an
alliance with Vegeta.
[GOKU] If that's
okay with you.
I was hoping that we can
join forces and work together
against those guys.
Well, how does that
sound to you, Vegeta?
Will you do it?
Yeah, sure, why not?
We're on it!
You got it, Goku!
Well, I guess
it's now or never.
What a magnificent
opportunity to showcase
my fabulous strength!
[NARRATOR] The battle
begins today.
Hmph!
Oh, no!
[GINYU] Ah-ha!
Huh?!
[GINYU] Ragh!
[GINYU] Yeeaah!
[GOKU] Whoa!
Huh?
Haa!
Agh!
[BOTH grunting]
Yah! Yah!
[GINYU laughs]
[grunting continues]
[GOKU shouts]
[GINYU shouts]
[GOKU grunts]
Ahh...!
Yah!
[GINYU laughs]
[GOKU yells]
Huh?!
[GOKU grunts]
[BOTH grunting,
blows landing]
Good show!
[JEICE] Ha, ha, ha,
way to go, eh!
Man, He packs a wallop!
My tooth is loose!
My, my what a rush!
Touché, this is a scream!
[GINYU laughs]
I had forgotten how much
fun a real fight could be!
[thinking] I can't let
this thing drag on!
Gohan and Krillin are
going to need my help!
I've got to do something!
[MONSTERS roaring]
[VEGETA chuckles]
This is just
too convenient!
Kakarot and Ginyu are back there
clobbering each other to death!
While the runts are up ahead
finding the Dragon Balls for me!
It's almost too
good to be true!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] I'll just wait until
those idiot Earthlings find out
what the password is,
then I'll step in
and make my wish instead.
You know, If I've
learned anything at all
from this silly ordeal, it's
that I am a freakin' genius!
[MONSTERS roaring]
Hey, after we
find the balls,
we need to ditch them
somewhere and find Guru!
Then we'll have to cross
our fingers and hope we can
make it back to the Dragon
Balls with the password
before Frieza finds us!
Right!
[GURU coughs]
[GINYU &amp; GOKU yell]
[GINYU] Allow me to
take a small break
to formally introduce myself!
Now, the leader of the Ginyu
Force, I am Captain Ginyu!
Hm?
[GOKU] Like this?
Yes-- No, no! Your left leg
is supposed to be up!
[GOKU] Hm?! Oh, I get it!
There!
But, heck, this pose. It
doesn't serve any real purpose!
[GINYU] What?!
Yeah, it's just a
silly waste of time!
What?! Waste of time?!
And I suppose you have
something better to do
Mr. Too-Busy-To-Show-
Off-Your-Pecks?!
That's right! Winning
this battle, for one!
I don't have all
day to stand around!
I've got places to be!
Oh, I'll tell you
where you're gonna be.
[GINYU laughs]
Listen up, buddy! The only
place you're gonna be...
is in a hospital
And by the way, I
know what you're up to!
Don't think that I
don't realize that
you're still concealing
the bulk of your power!
I'm not as gullible
as the others!
Hm?
That's right!
As a matter of fact, I, too,
share the coveted ability
to raise my fighting
power at will, you know.
Huh?!
[JEICE] That a boy, Cap'n!
He looks worried now!
You've got this bloke
right where you want 'im!
[thinking] Heh! I shoulda
known that the Cap'n
would take care
of business!
It looks like I'll
be getting my bonus
and two weeks paid
vacation after all!
[JEICE chuckles]
[GINYU growls]
[GOKU gasps]
[growling continues]
Huh?!
[GINYU yells]
[GINYU chuckles]
[GINYU] What a rush!
Man, that felt good!
[BULMA] If I wasn't
such a genius
and I didn't have
such a positive,
energetic personality,
this situation would
really be unbearable!
[BULMA] Hmm... Man,
here I am slaving away
for friends that
forgot I even exist.
It's a darn shame,
that's what it is!
Guess I shouldn't be
too surprised; those guys
are always taking
me for granted!
Hey, yo, diary!
[COMPUTER] Diary
loaded, please record.
Hi, me!
Just a reminder to kill Gohan
and Krillin when I see them!
And to kick Goku in the shin!
I guess that's it.
Huh?!
Ah! Wow, great!
Gosh, Bulma!
You are really just too much!
[distant rumbling]
[BULMA screams]
Hmm...?
[BULMA groans]
Wow, that's probably
gonna leave a lump...
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA] All seven Dragon
Balls are together!
Yikes, this could
be a serious problem!
On the other hand,
this could be perfect!
What a fantastic
opportunity to cash in on
someone else's hard work!
[BULMA] Hmm...
Ah...!
[thinking] What if the guys
come back for me and I'm gone,
so they leave?!
[distant rumbling]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA whimpers,
rumbling continues]
Hey, I know! I'll just wish
myself back! Yeah, that's it!
I'll ask the Dragon to
send me back to Earth!
Why didn't I think
of that before?
Alright, Dragon Balls,
here I come!
[GINYU chuckles]
[GINYU laughs]
[JEICE screams]
[JEICE] Wow, Captain!
What a whopper!
I haven't seen you get that
revved up since I came on board!
[GINYU] Quiet, Jeice.
I'm listening...
[GINYU chuckles]
[JEICE] Right, Captain!
Uhh, to what?!
[GINYU] Quiet...
Hm?!
[GOKU] Hah!
[GINYU] Aah!
[GINYU growls]
[grunting,
blows landing]
Huh?
Haah!
[GOKU] Huh?!
[GOKU] Haah!
--[GOKU shouting]
--Huh?!
[GINYU snarling]
Whoa! This guy's even
faster than me! Jerk...
Huh?
[GOKU] Woah!
[GOKU] Oh no!
[JEICE laughs]
Yeah! We did it, Cap'n!
[GOKU grunting]
[GINYU grunts]
[JEICE] Yeah, now
it's your turn, Cap'n!
Give him the final blow!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU shouts]
[grunting]
Man! Strong power...
can't shake it!
[JEICE] Hey, Cap'n!
This is one for the
record books, aye?!
I couldn't have
done it without you!
[thinking] Gotta think of
something fast or it's all over!
Woah!
Huh?
No, Captain!
We had him!
What in the world
did you do that for?!
I don't recall asking
for your help, Jeice!
[JEICE grunting]
But, sir! Why?! I--
Hush! You know better than
to interfere with my fight!
Do it again and you're through!
Do you hear me?! Finished!
[JEICE whimpering]
[GINYU] And as for you, Super
Slick, stop playing around!
Enough with this
bravado, I know
you're still hiding
your real power!
Maybe you're trying to save
it for when you meet Frieza?
Well, don't be a fool!
You'll never get by me
without baring your all!
Show me your perfect
power so that I can finally
test the depths of my strength
against a worthy opponent!
Come on, let's get right
to the nitty-gritty!
Well, what are you
waiting for, huh?!
I didn't know your friends
had so much time to spare!
Alrighty, then!
It'll give me a good workout,
and I can also save some time!
[GINYU] It would have come
to this anyway, besides,
this way is much more civil,
we don't have to get all
p!
bruised and beaten
You know you
don't have to
hurt other people
for amusement.
Helping people
can be fun too.
You should try
it sometime.
[GINYU laughs]
[GINYU] Oh, yes, yes,
I can see it now!
"Captain Ginyu,
protector of the weak
and the helpless
and the good!"
Look! Don't try to reform me.
Just show me your perfect power!
You betcha...
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[JEICE whimpers]
[grunting]
[GINYU chuckles]
[GOKU grunting]
[GINYU chuckling]
[GINYU gasps]
[GOKU yelling]
[JEICE whimpering]
[GINYU whimpering]
[GOKU growling]
housand
[GINYU] Ninety
and still rising!
Ahh! No way! But... how?!
[GOKU growling]
[GINYU] What?! One
hundred thousand!
I-I-I-I didn't
count on this!
This is completely insane!
[GOKU growling]
It's still going up!
Aaah!
[growling continues]
[GINYU] One hundred
and ten thousand!
[JEICE screams]
[growling continues]
Hey! Stop! Cut it out!
This just isn't my day!
[GOKU growling]
[GINYU whimpers]
[GINYU] I had you!
I had you in my hands!
I should have destroyed
you while I had the chance!
[JEICE whimpering]
[JEICE] With all due
respect, Captain,
this might be a good time
to go and get Frieza!
[GINYU] Shut up, Jeice!
I can handle this!
[NARRATOR] To the amazement
of Captain Ginyu,
Goku continues to
turn up the heat!
But will it be enough?
Tune in to the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!