[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan got a gift.
[GOHAN] ...press this
red button to make it work?
[BULMA] That's it.
[TRUNKS] Awesome!
Does it fit?
Yeah! Why...
it's a super fit!
[NARRATOR]
And when a high-jacked bus
went over a cliff,
it was time for
the new superhero
to spring into action!
That's right!
This bus stops here.
[VIDEL] Huh?!
[NARRATOR] Going up, anyone?
There's a new hero in town!
[GOHAN] I am...
guardian of the city!
The one and only!
[NARRATOR] That's right, Gohan!
Tell them how it is!
[GOHAN] The Great Saiyaman!
[GOHAN] I'm the Great Saiyaman!
Defender of truth!
Protector of the innocent!
Upholder of justice!
Doer of... good. Aah...
How come when Dad
said that kind of stuff
it just rolled
right off of his tongue
and sounded so natural.
[GOTEN] Gee, it sounded
okay to me, Gohan!
Nah! Thanks! Lets try this.
Here we go!
Protector of the innocent!
Defender of truth!
The light in the darkness!
I have come to crush
the oppressors of this world
once and for all!
All right, you! Unhand her!
Stand back! This is a job for...
The Great Saiyaman!
Well, whatd'ya think?
[GOTEN]
Yeah, that was awesome!
It sounded even better
than the superheroes on TV!
Can I be a superhero, too?
I think one superhero's
enough for now.
Mom, what'd you think?
Did you hear that?
I think it could
still use a little work.
But not tonight.
You've got to get up
bright and early tomorrow,
Great Saiyaman.
No problem, Mom. I'm fine.
[CHICHI] Gohan!
What are you doing?!
I thought you were
awake already!
School starts in ten minutes!
[GOHAN] Oh, man! I'm gonna
have to really move!
[school bell chimes]
Aah...
[GIRL]
Hi! I recognize you now!
You're in one of
my classes, aren't you?!
[GOHAN] Yeah! That's right!
Uh, English, isn't it?!
You know, it's about to start.
Aren't you worried
about being late?
[GIRL] No, not really.
[GOHAN]
You know... I can explain!
[GIRL] You can, huh?
[GOHAN laughs nervously]
[GOHAN] See you in class!
[GOHAN thinking] Ah, man!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Man! I really can't believe
I just did that!
I haven't even been
a superhero for a week
and I've already
blown my cover!
[GOHAN thinking] I'm so stupid!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
[GIRL thinking]
Wow! What an amazing guy!
And he's really cute, too!
[murmuring]
Gohan! You're on time!
Little miracles happen everyday!
[GOHAN sighs]
[door opens, closes]
Huh?!
[GIRL giggles]
--[GIRL] Mmm!
--[PROFESSOR] All right class,
let's continue where
we left off yesterday.
Now what did
Thoreau mean when he said:
"The mass of men lead lives
of quiet desperation." Videl?
[VIDEL]
I think that he meant that
most people are unhappy inside.
[PROFESSOR] Very good.
And what did he
attribute this to, Gohan?
[ERASA] Huh?
Is anybody home?
So... hm, we have a slacker.
[GOHAN] Oh, my gosh!
I shouldn't have landed there.
That was so stupid!
I'll bet the whole
school's going to know
by the end of the day!
[PROFESSOR] Gohan!
Huh? Aaah! Sir! What?!
[CLASSMATES chuckling]
So this is the way you
want it to be, huh, Gohan?!
I was expecting more from you!
Sir! Yes, sir!
[VIDEL sneezes]
[PROFESSOR] Listen up, class!
I don't give lashes or
make you wear a dunce-cap!
But after you hold those water
buckets for fifteen minutes,
you're going to wish I did!
Do you feel your shoulders
burning, Mister Gohan?!
Oh. Yes, sir.
[PROFESSOR] Good! Now who
can tell us what Thoreau felt
was causing the
inner desperation that he
sensed in his peers?
What do you think, Miss Angela?
[ANGELA sighs]
Miss Angela...
Hmm...
Let's start
with an easier question.
Angela, do you know
where you are?
Uh-huh.
All right, then! Spit it out!
Uh... I'm sorry, Professor!
I don't know!
I don't know anything!
[PROFESSOR] Uh, Angela,
perhaps you should, uh,
visit the counselor.
[ANGELA] No! No!
I need to be punished!
[PROFESSOR] Very well.
You can listen to the lecture
through the window
with Mister Gohan!
Okay, sir!
[PROFESSOR] Huh....?
[CLASSMATES murmur]
[ANGELA] Thanks, Professor!
My word!
[ANGELA] Hi.
Hi! You, too?
Yeah! Gosh!
I was naughty, too!
Yep! Mmm.
Ooh.
[ANGELA giggles]
[chuckles nervously]
[GOHAN thinking]
Oh, man! This is just great!
What am I going to do now?
--[ANGELA] Gohan!
--[GOHAN] Huh?
Uh... yeah? What?
Nothing! But do you have
a steady girlfriend?
No. I don't.
Wonderful!
How 'bout dating me then?!
Well, gosh! I... uh...
You think I'm ugly!
Don't you?!
Just say it!
You don't like me!
You think I'm ugly!
No! No! That's not true!
[ANGELA] Then why won't you go
out with me if it's not true?!
It's just...
If you don't go out with me,
I'll tell everyone your secret!
[GOHAN squeals] You wouldn't!
I sure would! Just try me!
Uh... Please don't!
[ANGELA] I don't understand!
Why won't you go out with me?
I thought we could start dating
and keep the secret between us!
But you don't like me!
That's not true!
Let's go out!
You really mean it?!
Yeah! [GOHAN chuckles]
Uh! Oh...
[ANGELA cheers, giggles]
Great! Great!
We are going to have a blast!
You just wait! Cool!
Eh...
Awesome! I'll see you
tomorrow then, okay?!
I'll meet you in front
of the train station
at one o'clock!
How did I get myself
into this predicament?!
Superheroes aren't
supposed to get blackmailed!
That just doesn't
happen that way.
What am I gonna do?
Maybe I should have Bulma
make me a different costume
and just call
myself something else!
How could I do this to myself?
I mean, I've never even
been on a date! This is crazy!
[CHICHI humming]
[door opens]
[GOHAN] Hey, Mom! I'm home!
[CHICHI] Hi, sweetheart!
How was your day?
[GOHAN] Pretty good!
Except that I have to
go out on a date tomorrow.
[CHICHI] You have to go?
That's a likely story.
You know that I'm sending you
to school to learn, Gohan.
You're going to need
your free time to study.
[GOHAN] No, I'm serious!
I have to go! She's forcing me!
Oh. Yes, I see!
I guess things
haven't changed that much
since I was a kid after all.
I remember the first time
I made your father
go out on a date with me.
[GOHAN] You made him?
Did you blackmail him?
[CHICHI] Oh, no! I don't think
I was that smart at the time.
I was just a little girl.
[YOUNG CHICHI giggles]
You know what? Gosh!
This feels like
we're just hanging out!
Is there anything special
we're supposed to do
since we're on a date?
Well, silly!
That's up to you!
You're the boy and
the boy is supposed to
think of the most
pleasurable thing to do
and then try to coax the girl
into doing it with him.
Oh, I think I get it now!
The most pleasurable thing!
Goku, you're so adorable!
[YOUNG CHICHI] Aaahhh!
[YOUNG GOKU yells]
[YOUNG GOKU laughs]
[YOUNG CHICHI yells]
[YOUNG GOKU]
Wow! This dating is fun!
[YOUNG CHICHI] Goku! This isn't
exactly what I had in mind!
[CHICHI sighs] You're father
was such a rowdy boy.
We spent the entire
day fighting.
What a great
first date that was!
Wow, gosh.
♪
Hm. Huh?
Hey! What's up?!
Thanks for coming!
You're so sweet! So, what are
we going to do today?!
Well, I've never been
on a date before.
Is there something
that you want to do?
Mmmnuuuuh...
Oh, well let's think about it.
Let's see here!
Hey! What about a movie?!
I love movies!
[GOHAN] Yeah, sure.
A movie sounds fun!
[ANGELA] Great!
It's settled then! Let's go!
[ANGELA] Come on, silly!
We're going to miss the start!
[CHAD] Listen, Loretta!
There's nothing
that can come between us.
Like, you're a great wave
in the ocean, y'know.
Once I get on it,
I know I'm gonna ride it
all the way in to shore, baby!
[LORETTA] And then the wave
crashes on the beach
and you go hop
on a different one!
Is that it?
[CHAD] What do you mean,
baby?! We're soulmates!
[LORETTA] I found your letter
to Katy, Chad!
You... ignoramus!
[CHAD]
Hey, wait, Loretta! Don't go!
You don't even wanna
be here with me!
Well, forget you!
--[GOHAN] No! Angela!
--[CHAD] That's not true,
--[GOHAN] That's not true! Uh!
--[CHAD] Loretta!
Wait! Angela!
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Hey! I'm sorry! Hold on!
Sorry! Pardon me. Excuse me.
Just comin' through here...
Angela! Wait up!
Hey! I'm sorry!
It's just that those
romance movies put me to sleep.
Whatd'ya say
we go get a coffee?!
Uhh...
[ANGELA giggles]
[ANGELA]
Isn't that hilarious?
[ANGELA laughs,
GOHAN chuckles]
See! You're not the only one
with secrets, silly boy!
I have my wild
side too, ya know!
Uh? Is that the same?
[ANGELA] Of course it is!
Oh, okay.
Hey, Gohan. I need
some sugar in my coffee.
Ten teaspoons, please!
[GOHAN] Nine...
Ten...
Thanks! That's why I'm so sweet!
[GOHAN]
Oh man! That's alot of sugar!
[ANGELA] Mm-hm! Yeah!
I actually have a
problem with mosquitos!
So, um, do you
have any other secrets
I should know about?
[GOHAN]
Huh? More secrets?
Oh, no. There's just the one!
[GOHAN chuckles]
[ANGELA] Well, I know I promised
I wouldn't say anything,
but can I tell my best friends?
No! A promise is a promise!
Mm! Okay!
I'll try my best, Gohan!
Please do.
[ANGELA] I'm really bad
at keeping secrets.
But for you, I'll do anything!
You believe me, don't you?
Uhh... well, yeah!
I don't have any reason
to doubt your word.
Gosh! You say
the cutest things!
[GOHAN] Oh, uh... But you do
realize what it would mean
if people knew that
it was me wearing that?
Yeah! Of course!
Stop worrying!
You're supposed
to be having fun!
Hey! Whatd'ya say
we go up to the top floor
of the City State Building!
Please?
Yeah. Sure.
[ANGELA] Mmm!
[ANGELA laughs,
GOHAN chuckles]
[distant sirens]
[BOTH] Huh?
[sirens continue]
[ANGELA] Oh no! Gohan, look!
That huge building is on fire!
[GOHAN] Sorry...
Hey? Gohan! Wait for me!
[sirens blaring,
CROWD murmuring]
[CROWD gasps]
[FIRECHIEF] Call for all units
in neighboring cities!
We need help!
[MAN 1] They say there are still
some people trapped up there!
[MAN 2] That is not good!
[WOMAN]
Look! Up there! It's Videl!
What's she doing?
[ANGELA] Uh...?
[CAPTIVE 1] Help us! Please!
Bring her down, Ed. Quick!
What? No way! No!
It's way too dangerous!
We can't help them
if we're dead!
We can't just let 'em fry!
Hey, Ed!
Check it out! Over there!
Isn't that a water tank?
[ED] Yeah! I think so!
That'd be my guess!
Come in, control.
I see a tank on the roof.
Isolate it. Go!
[CONTROL MAN]
We copy that, Videl!
I need to know
the contents and the amount.
[beeping]
Contents, eh, confirmed
to be water, Videl.
Amount confirmed to be
one-thousand gallons.
I'm now analyzing the outflow
and potential impact
on the fire.
[VIDEL] Is it enough to put
out the fire if I let it go?
Negative, Videl.
Plenty of water but that
building's gonna be melba toast
before you can
get that valve open.
[VIDEL]
It might not put it out,
but it will
buy us a little time.
No! Videl! Don't do it!
I can't just
leave 'em down there!
[ED] Videl! No!
[VIDEL grunts]
[VIDEL] Here we go!
Ah! [grunts]
[VIDEL] No pain, no gain!
[VIDEL grunts]
[WOMAN screams]
[CROWD gasps]
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?!
Stay here! And please don't
tell anyone about my secret!
Forget the stupid secret!
I just don't
want you getting hurt!
Oh, gosh. Thanks, Angela!
Just let me take care
of this real quick
and we'll go get an ice cream.
I'll be right back!
[FIREMAN]
Please stay on the other
--[ANGELA] Okay!
--[FIREMAN] side of the barrier!
Errrgh! Come on, you!
[VIDEL] Come on,
you stubborn thing!
Whoa! This is it!
[CAPTIVES yelling]
[VIDEL] Oh, no you don't!
Where do you
think you're goin'? Huh?!
[VIDEL screams]
[GOHAN grunts]
[VIDEL] Huh?!
[GOHAN] Excuse me, miss!
Please clear out!
Huh?! You...
At your service!
[VIDEL] Saiyaman! There's
enough water in the tank
to put out the fire
but the release valve
can't let it all go in time!
Thank you.
[GOHAN] Stand back, everyone!
[CROWD murmuring, gasping]
[CROWD gasping]
Yeah!
[CROWD cheering]
All right! It's a miracle!
[MAN 3] Look! Up there!
It's that guy! Saiyaman!
[CROWD cheering]
[VIDEL thinking] Saiyaman, huh?
I'll find out
who you really are!
[FIRECHIEF] All right, folks!
The fun's over!
Please clear the area!
[FIREMAN 2] Send the ambulatory
units home, Sergeant!
We got lucky!
[SERGEANT] Yes, sir!
While I was opening the valve,
the roof started
collapsing--hm?!
Hold on one second.
[VIDEL] Where are
you going, Gohan?!
[GOHAN] Eh. Huh?
So what's the rush? Huh?!
Rush? I wasn't rushing!
[GOHAN chuckles nervously]
Gohan, you're hiding
something, aren't you?!
Uh. What d'ya mean?
Hiding what?!
Uuh...
[ANGELA gasps]
No!
--[VIDEL] Huh?
--[GOHAN] Huh? Hey!
I've been looking for you!
You lied to me! Shame, shame!
[GOHAN] Huh?
You-You didn't have anything
that you needed
to take care of!
You saw Videl
and you wanted to sneak off
and meet her
and give her a kiss!
[GOHAN]
Angela! That's not true!
And I really
liked you, Gohan!
I can't believe you would
embarrass me like this!
Videl, how would you like
to know a little secret
about Gohan that only I know?!
Sure, why not?
Aaah! Angela, no!
Look! See what
he's wearing?!
Mm-hmm.
[GOHAN screams]
He's hiding
something underneath!
Mm-hmm.
[GOHAN screams]
He's wearing
some underwear that
only a three-year old
would wear!
[GOHAN sceams]
[ANGELA screams]
Your secret. That's it?
No!
[ANGELA] Don't you
deny it, Gohan! I saw them!
It was the day
before yesterday, pal!
[GOHAN] Wait.
The day before yesterday?
[ANGELA] Yes! I was
on my way to gym class,
minding my own business,
when I noticed that
Gohan was still
in the locker room.
He was pulling up
his pants and I saw it.
[ANGELA] It was the cutest
teddy-bear I'd ever seen!
How adorable! Gosh!
Fess up! You wear
teddy-bear underwear!
That's my secret
that you've been keeping?
Until now!
What about when we
were both on the roof yesterday
right before our English class
was about to start?
Oh, that? Oh, no! Not then!
I couldn't have
seen your underwear then
because I didn't
have my contacts in.
Were your pants down?
[GOHAN yells]
I thought you were a nice boy!
Keep your pants on!
Or else! Got it?!
No! [laughs nervously]
That's not what I meant!
Of course I didn't have my
pants off on the roof yesterday!
Don't be silly, you two!
[ANGELA] I don't
like you anymore, Gohan!
Ooh.
[ANGELA] See if I ever
let you take me out again!
I feel so bad!
Angela really liked me
and somehow I managed
to hurt her feelings!
I'll bet I destroyed
her whole world! Man...
[GOHAN thinking]
I feel terrible!
I need to find her
and apologize!
Huh?
No way! That's my sign, too!
Wow! We have
alot in common then!
And what a physique!
The last guy I went out with
was nice but he was whimpy!
He even wore
teddy-bear underwear!
--[GUY] No way!
--[ANGELA] Yes!
[GOHAN chuckles nervously]
[NARRATOR] As another day
begins at Orange Star High,
the true identity of the Great
Saiyaman remains a mystery.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z!