[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z,
chaos reigned in the
cities as ordinary citizens
had been turned into evil
maniacs by the Black Water Mist!
Animals and humans alike were
infected by the dreaded mist!
Needless to say, this is
one game of cat and mouse
that we all hope
we never have to play!
[NARRATOR]
Atop of Kami's Lookout,
the battle that would
determine the fate
of the earth continued!
And it looked like
Piccolo was up to the task!
But even though Kami was free
and had the
Sacred Water in hand,
Garlic Jr. still
had the last laugh.
There wasn't enough
time to spread the remedy
over the earth
before the changes
from the Black Water
Mist became permanent!
[POPO] We might
still have a chance, Kami.
[NARRATOR] Luckily, Mr. Popo
knew of a way to beat the clock,
but the plan meant putting
Kami's life in jeopardy!
While Kami and Mr. Popo
set off on their mission
to distribute the Sacred Water,
Garlic Jr. squared off
against Piccolo!
I want to
show you something...
My source of power!
[NARRATOR] Piccolo was no
stranger to Garlic Jr.'s ability
to transform
into a powerful giant.
But with the proximity
of the Makyo Star,
Garlic Jr.'s powers
were at their zenith!
[grunts]
[NARRATOR] And so the
incredible transformation began,
and the pesky elf of evil
became a titan of terror,
right before
Piccolo's very eyes!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, Kami and Mr. Popo
were walking on thin ice
as unwelcome guests
at the ancient burial ground
of guardians past!
Can Kami accomplish his mission
without losing his life?
Find out, today!
[NARRATOR]
High above the earth,
Kami's once beautiful
sanctuary now stands in ruin
as the evil light
from the Makyo Star
shines down from above!
[chuckles]
[SPICE and VINEGAR laugh]
[SPICE] Yeah, that's our boss!
[KRILLIN] Oh man. From blue
dwarf to green giant! Yikes!
[VINEGAR]
It's not over yet, kids!
We're just
getting started!
[SPICE] Yeah,
feast your eyes on this!
[yells]
[SPICE and VINEGAR yelling]
[SPICE bellows]
[BOTH bellow]
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
Skyscrapers!
[GOHAN] Man o' man!
There! Allow us
to show you twerps
what the Spice Boys
are made of!
[laughs, grunts]
[BOTH] Huh?
Hm?
[KRILLIN groans]
[yells]
You!
Ha! Peek-a-boo!
Come to big daddy Garlic!
Huh?
[chuckles]
[GARLIC JR.] What's the matter?
You look a little
stressed out, Piccolo!
[chuckles]
[KAMI] I'm not sure what
that spirit did, Mr. Popo.
But for some reason I'm
having trouble staying awake.
[POPO] Please, Kami!
You have to fight it!
If you go to sleep in this
place, you'll never wake up!
Kami!
[MALE VOICE]
Leave him alone!
Let him rest! Can't you
see how weary he is?
You know what it means
when a guardian of the earth
passes through
those gates, Mr. Popo!
[POPO] That voice!
Kami! Your predecessor!
What?
Are you sure, Mr. Popo?
[POPO]
Yes, Kami! Absolutely!
So, Popo. You recognize me?
Yes, your guardianship.
I am happy to see you.
[POPO] It's been such
a long time! I've missed you!
[MALE VOICE] You shouldn't have
brought Kami here, Mr. Popo!
You know that!
Kami! He's gone!
[gasps]
He hasn't changed! My word!
Nothing could ever penetrate
that thick head of his!
[MALE VOICE] What?
Please, your guardianship!
Surely you know the predicament
that the earth is in!
Please, sir!
Just this one time!
Kami! Hold on!
[BOTH groan]
Please, I beg of you!
If you don't allow us
to release the Sacred Water
from up here, it will
never spread in time!
[KAMI] The people of Earth
will be permanently altered
by the Black Water Mist!
This is our only chance! Please!
Oh, no! Kami, lookout!
[POPO yells]
My word! You're smoking,
Mr. Popo! Are you all right?
[POPO] Don't worry
about me, Kami. I'm fine!
But what now? He's not
going to let us through, Kami!
I know him. Once he makes up
his mind, it's all over.
[POPO] I'm afraid our
mission here is hopeless.
We'll be lucky to
get out of here alive!
[KAMI] Get ready, Mr. Popo!
Let's break for it! Come on!
[POPO] Huh?
[KAMI] C'mon, Mr. Popo!
Run like crazy!
[grunts]
[VINEGAR grunting]
[SPICE grunts]
Why you!
[BOTH yell]
Kami!
[KAMI] Faster, Popo!
[POPO] Yes, Kami!
[VINEGAR yells]
[KRILLIN groans]
Well! Fancy that!
[chuckles]
[VINEGAR]
Hey! Found a meatball!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
You're dead, bone head!
[VINEGAR grunting]
Ha! Kick-off time!
[VINEGAR grunts]
Oh, no! Krillin!
[GOHAN] Krillin!
Huh? Aah!
[GOHAN] Krillin, no...!
[BOTH chuckle]
[GOHAN] Krillin!
Krillin...!
[GOHAN] No...!
No!
[yells]
No way!
Darn! Yes way!
Oh, no!
[VINEGAR and SPICE yell]
[GOHAN] Krillin!
[GARLIC JR. grunts]
The end of Piccolo...
[chuckles] ...and Kami!
[laughs]
[chuckles]
[GARLIC JR.] I guess
Piccolo wasn't exactly
the pillar of strength
he made himself out to be!
[laughs] Hm?
[GARLIC JR.]
Hm... What a kid!
[GARLIC JR.] I wouldn't
believe it if I hadn't
experienced it myself!
[GARLIC JR.] Congratulations!
You've made the first cut!
It's too bad,
but your friend Piccolo
wasn't as fortunate as you.
[grunts]
Hm! It's a shame!
Isn't it, kid? Tough luck!
[chuckles]
[GARLIC JR.]
You're mad, aren't you?
What are you
going to do about it?
[GARLIC JR. growls]
Huh?
[GOHAN] Piccolo! Ha, ha, ha!
You're all right!
Yeah, I'm fine!
[PICCOLO] This over-stuffed
dwarf can't win.
You think you're so big!
Well how about taking on
someone your own size? Like me!
[grunts, yells]
[yells]
[GOHAN]
Wow! Piccolo! Unbelievable!
I didn't know he could
expand his size like that!
Your power's increased.
And you're big. But you're slow!
You can't sacrifice speed
for power! Not against me!
[grunts]
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH] Ooh!
Popo, there's a wall.
Yes, Kami, I forgot.
I'm afraid we can not
go any farther than this.
Not without the former
guardian's permission!
[KAMI groans]
Kami! Please turn back now!
Or he'll never let us
out of here alive!
Then so be it.
[yells]
That wasn't so bad.
Kami! Wow!
[KAMI] Head for the hills!
[POPO] Kami! Were you hit?
[KAMI] No, it's not that.
[gasps]
No! Fight it!
[KAMI] I'm trying, Mr. Popo,
but I'm feeling
a little light headed.
And, light-handed!
Kami! You can do it!
I believe in you!
Don't give up, please!
Very well, Mr. Popo.
Kami!
[PICCOLO groans]
What happened?
[GOHAN] Piccolo, what's wrong?
I know. It's that
idiotic bird-brain.
[GARLIC JR.]
You're losing power, aren't you?
Yes, that's it! Kami!
He must be having his soul
stripped away as we speak!
[POPO] Kami, wait!
I sense something ahead!
[BOTH yell]
[KAMI groans]
[PICCOLO groans]
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
You've finally
come to your senses!
[GARLIC JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO groans]
[KAMI] No, I can't give up!
[yells]
[POPO] Kami, wait!
There's another wall ahead!
[KAMI] Can't stop now, Popo!
But we're about to hit it!
[KAMI yells]
[POPO] Kami! Wait for me!
Can't move!
Oh, Kami! Your body! Look!
[KAMI]
Yes, I see, Mr. Popo.
Not good...
[GARLIC JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO groans]
[GARLIC JR. grunting]
Hey! What's wrong?
[KRILLIN] Gohan...!
Gohan. Look.
Piccolo's losing power.
I-I think something terrible
has happened to Kami!
H... Help him!
Krillin...
[groans]
Oh, yeah! Death blow!
That's right! Time's up!
Oh... Kami, look!
I'll be darned!
That's it, Mr. Popo!
[KAMI] The hole above the
world's seven air-currents!
[POPO] I can't believe it,
Kami! We really did it!
[POPO] Kami! Kami! No! Please!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
It's the bottom of
the ninth for you, Piccolo!
And here's the pitch!
[GARLIC JR.] Strike three!
You're out of there!
It's the end
of the game! You lose!
[groans]
[yells]
[grunts]
[growls lowly]
[NARRATOR] Kami and Mr. Popo
are just a stone's throw away
from reaching their goal,
but suddenly,
their destination seems
so very far away!
Does Kami have the
strength of will to defy
the former guardians
so that he can release
the Sacred Water in time?
[NARRATOR] Kami's predicament
has Piccolo down for the count,
and it's all
boiling down to this.
[NARRATOR] The battle for
the earth is between Gohan...
and Garlic Jr.!
What can Gohan do to defeat a
being armed with eternal life?!
Find out, on the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!