[NARRATOR] On the last episode
of Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu became furious
when his every attempt to
defeat the powered-up Gohan
proved useless.
Gohan was clearly
the superior fighter,
and it seemed Buu's
destructive spree
would at last come to an end.
[NARRATOR] But the crazed Buu
put an abrupt stop to the fight
by turning himself
into a living bomb,
apparently trying
to take Gohan with him.
[NARRATOR]
Gohan survived,
and in the following calm,
lost friends were reunited.
[PICCOLO] You're alive.
I don't know how you did it.
[NARRATOR]
But a dark cloud on the horizon
put a damper on the reunion,
as Majin Buu returned from
hiding, only one hour later...
[NARRATOR] ...and delivered
a puzzling request.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
Come on then, little worms.
I want to fight you now!
[ALL gasp]
[GOHAN]
That is not gonna happen!
You're fighting me, Buu.
You got it?
What happened boys? Don't tell
me you're scared to fight Buu.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN growl]
[SUPER BUU]
You were raring to go before.
[NARRATOR] What sinister
trick does Majin Buu
have hiding behind his back?
Find out now, on Dragon Ball Z!
[TRUNKS, GOTEN grunting]
[SUPER BUU chuckling]
Oh I'm sorry,
I must of misjudged you.
What's he saying?
I think he's trying
to say we're weak!
Then I guess he doesn't
remember us kicking his butt.
I wouldn't say we're
down for the count just yet.
We just thought
Gohan deserved a shot.
[SUPER BUU]
Ah, I see,
for a moment I thought
you were hiding behind him.
Now why don't you do your little
magic so we can get started?
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Fine!
Ha, I'm ready.
With Gohan on our side,
there's no way we'll get beat.
Yeah, and I'm sick and tired
of hearing this pink guy
run his big, goofy mouth!
[PICCOLO] Goten, Trunks,
hold your ground for a moment.
I'm sensing some kind of...
...deception.
C'mon, Piccolo,
you gotta be kidding.
he's not smart enough
for something like that.
He can't even spell deception.
Let's go!
No! Come back!
[GOTEN] Hey, you can't
spell that word, either.
[TRUNKS]
Shut up!
There, you got what
you asked for, Majin Buu.
Gotenks is back in the ring!
[GOHAN]
No, Trunks, you two stay back.
I'm dealing with this myself.
[GOTEN] But, ah, come on!
We're really good.
[squelching]
[TRUNKS]
This stinks!
We can't just stand here
and watch. I wanna fight!
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
[growling]
[BEE barks]
Don't worry about
a thing, Gohan,
you haven't seen me
and Trunks in action yet.
When we do fusion,
we're unbeatable!
Watch this, okay?
[SUPER BUU thinking]
That's it boys.
Do your little fusion for me.
Now, are you ready, Goten?
Yeah!
[GOTEN] This time, we
should definitely start off
as Super Saiyan Three!
Fu...
...sion!
Ha!
Whoa, so that's
what fusion looks like.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[GOTENKS]
Yeah!
Sorry you were
missing me, ugly,
but now I'm back,
and stronger than ever.
Now, that's weird.
First there were two kids,
and now there's one,
and he's got blonde hair
instead of... What's goin' on?!
[SUPER BUU thinking]
The power of Gotenks
and the mind of Piccolo.
Unstoppable.
[squelching]
[squelching continues]
[barks]
[MR. SATAN] It just doesn't
make sense to me.
If two kids became one,
uh, they'd be twice as big.
--Right?
--[BEE growling]
Look, I'm pretty hungry too, but
right now, there's this fight.
And I'm tryin' to figure out
this other thing
all at the same time.
[barks]
Well, Gohan,
I hope you don't mind
if I take it from here.
You're looking like you
could use a little break.
[chuckles]
I'll beat on Buu
for a little while.
[grunts]
Then, I might be nice enough to
give you another shot at him.
Nice attitude, you've definitely
got some Vegeta in you.
[GOTENKS]
Thank you.
[SUPER BUU growls]
[chuckles]
[barks]
Wait, Bee! You're
running the wrong way!
[BEE barking]
[MR. SATAN]
Bee! No!
I-If you keep
running that way,
you'll end up
killing both of us!
[gasps]
[squelching]
[MR. SATAN]
Hey, that's weird! Huh?!
[gasping]
[GOTENKS] How 'bout I give
you the first move?
Ah!
[GOTENKS groaning]
Ah! What is that?!
[GOTENKS] Uh! Hey!
Get this nasty goo off of me!
[groaning] Stop it!
[PICCOLO grunting]
No, not Piccolo!
[MR. SATAN groaning]
Guys, stay close,
you'll be safer!
[PICCOLO groans]
[GOTENKS groans]
Yes! Come to me!
[GOHAN]
No! What's he doing to them?!
Man, this looks bad!
You know what's happening?
Quick, Gohan, Raise your power!
He's changing again!
[gasping]
[SUPER BUU groaning]
[groaning continues]
[gasping]
No, he absorbed them.
[MR. SATAN gasping]
[MR. SATAN]
Does that mean he's gonna
run around and absorb us all?
He might. He went after
Gotenks and Piccolo,
so we know he's absorbing
the bravest fighters.
Uh, I hope he doesn't
find us back here.
So, Gohan, what
do you think of it?
New clothes to match my figure,
and a few new abilities as well!
[grunts]
I suppose the sudden loss
of your friends and family
has left you speechless, Gohan.
Hurry and drain your
tears so we can fight.
[chuckles]
How could you do that to them?
They've been fair in
this fight since the start.
I'm not interested in fairness,
I'm interested in the extinction
of every living creature
on this planet.
A good fighter knows his mental
and physical limitations,
but a great fighter will
figure a way around them.
From the moment I felt your
power, I knew I was beaten.
And then I thought
about something,
if I could hatch a plan to
absorb Piccolo and Gotenks
and their powers,
then no force on this
boring, pathetic planet
would ever stand a chance
against me again.
And then another important
factor was revealed. Time...
[GOTENKS]
I've only got five more minutes,
then we'll have to wait an hour
until I can do fusion again!
You'd be smart
to show your face.
Here I am about to lose
all of my powers,
and be helpless to
defend myself. Really!
It's just poor,
little Gotenks here,
all by his lonesome,
unable to fight back at all.
[SUPER BUU] Individually, the
boys were worthless to me,
but together, they have the
strength to make me invincible.
So, I decided to
wait out the hour
until they could do their
little fusion trick again.
Then all I had to do
was get them angry.
Tch. Well, you got
me angry, too.
You know,
if you wanted the best,
you should've come after me.
You just absorbed the
wrong Super Saiyans, Buu.
And if you're using
Piccolo's brains,
you know you've
got thirty minutes
until this newfound
strength of yours defuses.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
I assure you, it will
be over before then.
And I didn't absorb you
because I needed a punching bag.
What's the point
of having strength
if there's nothing to hit?
I kept you around because
I'm stronger than ever,
and I have to try it on someone.
Sounds fine, I'm all yours.
Let's do this.
All right,
but be warned,
in my new super form
I have the body of Buu,
the intensity of Gotenks,
and all the cunning of a Namek
ready to drive the nails
into your coffin.
I'm tougher than Gotenks
and smarter than Piccolo.
So, I guess, the only thing
you have to worry about
is if I'm stronger than you.
[gasping]
You know I'm going
to kill you, Gohan.
Well let's hold off on
the gravestone, Majin Buu.
[GOHAN, SUPER BUU grunting]
[BOTH groan]
Uh?!
Uh!
[SUPER BUU groans]
[grunts]
[yells]
[SUPER BUU screaming, groans]
[gasps]
[yells]
[grunting]
[growls]
[GOHAN groaning]
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[grunting]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[GOHAN pants]
[SUPER BUU] That was fun, Gohan.
Why don't we try it again?
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[MR. SATAN] Where-- where
are all the army guys?
I thought they
were droppin' bombs.
There's no army. Gohan and
Majin Buu are fighting.
All those explosions
from two guys?
They don't even look like
they've taken a single punch.
Do you think Buu's
gonna come after me?
Uh-huh, if you're a strong guy,
I think he might.
Do you not know who I am?
I am Mr. Satan,
Champion of the World
Martial Arts Tournament,
and the savior of planet
Earth, gotta fan club.
Well, he'll surely
be looking for you.
[SUPER BUU] It seems you're
weaker than you thought.
Is your confidence
dwindling yet?
There's no shame
in quitting here.
You can just walk away
whenever you want.
Your mind games aren't
gonna work on me, Buu.
I've been trained
much better than that.
Now let's go again!
All right, it's time to show you
why my little brother
looks up to me.
He doesn't.
If fact, he wonders
why you let me take him.
[grunts]
[SUPER BUU] Oh, I bet
that hurts, doesn't it?
Ah!
[SUPER BUU] Your old teacher
Piccolo isn't impressed, Gohan.
He thought you were
smarter than that.
[GOHAN groans]
[SUPER BUU] And Trunks thinks
you're a cowardly deserter,
just like your father.
[laughing]
--[SUPER BUU growls]
--[GOHAN groans]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[GOHAN screams]
[SUPER BUU grunts, chuckles]
[groans]
Gohan, look up!
[screams]
[MR. SATAN, DENDE groaning]
Gohan, where are you?
Elder Kai, Gohan just
vanished while he was fighting.
Does he still have the
ability to defeat Majin Buu?
Mm.... Beats me.
--[SUPREME KAI] Ee!
--[GOKU gasps]
Everything is falling apart.
I can't seem to find
him anywhere. Is he...?
Don't even think like
that okay? He's alive!
[gasping]
I tell you,
I think this fight's over.
Remember, not so long ago,
I was the one hiding.
I needed time to stall.
Is that what you're
doing now, Gohan?
Are you hiding, trying to think
your way out of this mess?
You seem to have forgotten
that your beloved Piccolo
is a part of me,
and I can sense that
you're alive down there, kid.
[NARRATOR] After absorbing
both Piccolo and Gotenks,
Buu's physical
and mental abilities
have reached a new pinnacle.
Will Gohan's training hold up
in the face of this
newly formed Super Buu?
[GOHAN]
Buu!
[yells]
[NARRATOR] Stay tuned for scenes
from the next, Dragon Ball Z!