[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
after destroying most
of the Earth's population,
Majin Buu was led to the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber
earlier than expected,
demanding that he face his
long-promised challenger.
Those kids?
[PICCOLO]
That's right.
[NARRATOR]
But with minutes bought
by Piccolo's bold distractions,
the boys had enough time to
perfect their fusion training!
This is the end for you!
Majin Buu!
Let's begin!
Fu-sion!
Ha!
[NARRATOR] And in a
blinding flash of light,
Majin Buu's
challenger was created.
Gotenks had returned.
[NARRATOR] The war for planet
earth's few survivors has begun,
with Gotenks at the helm!
But still Majin Buu
stands unscathed.
[GOTENKS thinking]
So much for the plan.
After that kind of attack,
he's not even bruised.
I'll just have to show
him a few of my secrets.
The battle continues today!
Foolish, they should have become
Super Saiyans before they fused.
This won't, take long,
earthlings are weak.
Not me, I just gotta
get warmed up first.
Then I'm deadly.
[gasps]
This next move is a new
one I've been working on,
tell me what you think.
A nuclear kick!
[pants]
Now, that worked well.
[GOTENKS]
Detonate!!
[SUPER BUU]
So you made smoke?
Looks like this is
going to take a while.
You better prepare yourself
for the spindletop punch!
Wait!
[GOTENKS]
Huh?
Not there.
Try my face.
Don't tell me how to fight!
[GOTENKS] How 'bout a chopper
on your chops, wimp!
That's it!
[GOTENKS]
Charging mad bull attack!
A swinging disaster blaster!
[GOTENKS]
Reverse double dropkick!
Stinging Tommy-gun punch!
[GOTENKS]
Quick darting ankle-blast!
Gotenks!
Wait. What's the next move?
[GOTENKS]
Exploding snake attack!
Ultimate twin elbow combo!
Flying bluejay assault!
Screaming angry wombat.
Screaming angry wom--!
Ah!!
Ow!
That hurt!
We're doomed.
[GOTENKS] So, it looks like
you can take hits pretty well.
You're a lot stronger than you
were the last time we fought.
But I've planned for that...
Oww, it keeps throbbing!
Huh?
Need a couple of minutes.
Piccolo, be honest,
do you think that there's any
way that I can beat this guy?
I think there's a way
to succeed in everything,
you just have to
be serious about it.
That's no answer!
I... Uh...
Hey!
I'm throwing punches
as hard as I can,
pulling out every
trick in the book
and even a handful
that I just made up.
You made up what?
My own moves!
That is what real
warriors do, you know!
Plus, I've been thinking
about some new strategies
that might work later.
[PICCOLO]
Oh, is that so?
And what particular strategies
did you have in mind?
[GOTENKS] Well, usually
you take a beating,
wearing the other guy down
until you turn the tables on him
at the end and finish him off.
But I've been attacking
in a way that makes him think
I'm a lot weaker
than I actually am
because I've got a
huge trick up my sleeve.
Get it?
[PICCOLO]
Gotenks, why didn't you attack
with your full strength
from the beginning?
[GOTENKS]
What?!
Because, I want
people to remember this
as something unique,
not just another brawl.
[PICCOLO]
Cut the nonsense!
Do you understand that the
fate of the world rests
on your ability to beat him?
[SUPER BUU]
All you people do is TALK!
Fine! Then let the
second round begin!!
Haaa!
[PICCOLO thinking]
He better do it right this time.
[KRILLIN]
Man, I hope Trunks and Goten
had enough training
time in there.
[ROSHI]
Did you see that guy, Krillin?
No amount of training
is gonna be enough
to beat something like that.
Quiet! This is hard enough
without you two making it worse!
How do you think I feel?
You think I don't
know their chances?
I know they might not survive!
And I know Piccolo might destroy
the door and trap them in there!
But they can be revived
with everyone else
using the Dragon Balls.
But what if they're not dead?
What if they simply
lose the fight?
Do you expect Piccolo
to kill them and himself?
Well, I don't know about you,
but I absolutely hate the idea
of my son's mentor murdering him
so he can come back to life.
Can you understand that?
[PICCOLO thinking]
Please tell me that move was
part of his plan.
[SUPER BUU]
Feeling dizzy?
I've had enough!
I should be
fighting great warriors!
There's nothing
great about you.
Is that so?
'Cause I've got a secret.
I've been using
a little strategy.
And I'm stronger than you think.
Nice move, huh?
You know if I was you,
I'd start running about now.
Yes!
Su--
--per--
Saiyan!
[snickers]
Hmm?
I had no idea you could become
a Super Saiyan after fusing.
[GOTENKS thinking]
Yeah, that's much better.
Majin Buu has no
idea what I just did
now I'll kick this up a notch.
Good, we may
still have a chance!
[GOTENKS] Time to put all
the goofing around to an end.
[GOTENKS]
What do you say, ugly?
Are you ready?
[GOTENKS] But I'm, not
exactly sure which of my moves
I should throw out first.
I'll save some for later
but I have to use
a good one right now.
He's getting impatient,
Gotenks, get up!
All right, got it.
But this particular move might
cut him in half, which is fine!
The cosmic halo!
Stop!
Down!
He's got him!
Looks painful.
You know,
I'd give you a breather,
but it feels pretty
good from this end!
[chuckles]
Watch this.
[gasps]
He's too strong.
[GOTENKS]
Uh-oh.
Ha ha ha ha!
Just what I thought you'd do.
Your moves are so predictable.
If you really think that, then
you would have your guard up.
Missed me!
[SUPER BUU]
Wrong.
Wait, hold on.
Well that could
have ended better.
That wasn't me.
Get out of the tub.
Hey, it's not like we
both couldn't use a bath.
[PICCOLO]
You got my cape soggy.
[GOTENKS]
Come here!
It's time for a serious move.
I've had enough of this!
Heads up!!
Hey, Majin Butt!
How's that headache feeling?!
[growls]
So you're not completely
indestructible are you, big guy?
You know, I've
got a certain move
I've been saving
for this exact moment.
I hope you enjoy it!
[GOTENKS] It's new so sorry
if it's a little sloppy.
A Super Ghost Kamikaze attack!
[gasps]
[PICCOLO] Come on Gotenks
let's try something that works.
Ha!
What the heck...
...is that thing...?
Hi! Ready, Buu?
[NARRATOR]
As strange as it sounds,
Gotenks has burped
out what appears
to be a ghost of himself.
Is this part of the
brand new technique
he's been bragging about?
And if it is,
what exactly does it do?
Stay tuned for more excitement,
on Dragon Ball Z!
You're dead.