[NARRATOR] It looked to be
lights out for Vegeta
on the last episode
of Dragon Ball Z,
until the World Martial
Arts Champion himself
stepped in to
challenge Majin Buu!
[NARRATOR] The champ was
cruisin' for a bruisin',
but when Buu tried to attack,
he became crippled with agony!
Until, he hocked up the
source of his pain, that is,
and spit it out for good!
[NARRATOR]
It was the gentle Buu.
And now that his kind influence
had been expectorated,
the evil Buu was going to
make Hercule dead! But wait!
[BUU] You leave alone!
Him Buu's buddy!
[NARRATOR]
And so, the battle between
the good and evil Buu's began.
Meanwhile, Goku attempted
to gather enough energy
to join the action!
[GOKU] I need to relax.
Let go. I'm way too tense!
[NARRATOR]
It was a horrifying sight to see
the great Super Saiyan Three
completely sapped of his power.
Can there be any
hope of victory now?
[growls]
[MR. SATAN] Get him, Buu!
Yeah, come on, pow!
[barking]
[GOKU gasping]
Hey! What's the deal?
Were you playing some kind
of stupid joke on me, or what?
That didn't tickle, you know!
[panting]
Sorry, I misjudged.
Man, how strange!
When I was training
in Other World,
Super Saiyan Three
was, well, easy!
But this body, it chugs.
Yeah, I'll bet it uses
twice as much energy.
Wait a minute, guess
you're pretty mad.
[KID BUU grunts]
[BUU groans]
[MR. SATAN]
Buu!
--[MR. SATAN gasping]
--[BEE barking]
[KID BUU grunts]
--[KID BUU laughs]
--[BUU groans]
--[MR. SATAN gasping]
--[BEE barking]
--[MR. SATAN] Buu!
[MR. SATAN]
Unhand him, you scoundrel!
Lousy runt! How dare
you hurt my friend!
I'm gonna turn you inside out!
[MR. SATAN grutning]
[MR. SATAN groans]
[BEE barks]
Ah! Turn you into chocolate!
[BUU]
Huh?!
[KID BUU chuckles]
[screams]
[BUU]
Bad little Buu!
[BUU, KID BUU grunting]
He can't even land
a punch. Come on, Buu.
Hang in there. Don't die!
[VEGETA thinking]
Darn it!
We can't overpower him,
we're just going to
have to outsmart him!
[VEGETA thinking] There's
got to be a way! But how?
[VEGETA gasps]
Supreme Kai! Dende! Old Kai!
If you're listening to me, I
need to talk to you right now!
Uh?!
[VEGETA] I need your assistance!
Come on, can you hear me or not?
[ALL gasp]
[OLD KAI]
Yes, yes! We're here.
Good! Now, look. Go to the
new planet Namek right away!
Quick, there's no time to waste!
Gather the Dragon Balls.
[DENDE]
I'll have to tell them what for.
To save our hides!
That's what for!
But if you don't hurry,
it'll be too late!
[OLD KIAI]
The Dragon Balls?
We can't use them to
settle our affairs.
[DENDE] But Sir, Vegeta needs
them! He must have a plan.
Plan schmann! No can do.
But this isn't our affair!
Don't you see? It's everyone's.
And if we don't do everything
in our power to help,
we're as guilty as Buu.
All right! Take it easy!
You made your point.
Now, let's get going.
[DENDE]
Thank you, Sir.
Well, it's about time.
Hey, I know you've got a plan.
[VEGETA]
Yes! And?!
Well, I hate to pry, but,
um, what is it, exactly?
Kakarot, how many times have you
saved the world up till now?
Hm. What? How many?
I'm not sure.
[VEGETA]
Just a ballpark.
Well, gosh! Half a
dozen, at least!
[VEGETA]
Then perhaps it's time
to let the world fend
for itself, for once.
[gasps]
[DENDE]
Wow! It's just as I remember.
Hmm? Not bad! Nice, short grass.
Uh. Yes, but where is everybody?
This is too good to be true!
It even smells the same!
Ahh! My beautiful home!
[MOORI]
Well, it's good to see
you haven't forgotten
about us all together.
Feeling a bit homesick
perhaps, Dende?
--[OLD KIAI] Hm? Oh!
--[DENDE laughs]
[DENDE]
Moori! It's really you!
[NAMEKS murumur]
[DENDE] Hi, everybody!
It's good to see you all again!
Elder, you truly are
the picture of wisdom
and good health.
Oh, Dende! You've grown into
a strong and noble guardian.
Haven't you, my boy?
Well, sort of!
The planet I was guarding,
it, kind of, met with a
little accident and blew up.
[OLD KAI]
Excuse me!
I hate to interrupt
your lovely reunion,
but we do have something
of a crisis on our hands.
Yes, very true.
Elder! We're in danger!
Please, help us out!
Sir, with your permission,
we need to summon Porunga
as soon as possible!
Hmm... I See, well, uh...
You know our rules concerning
the use of the Dragon Balls.
I'm surprised that you would
make such a request, Dende.
[DENDE]
But, Sir!
[MOORI]
Yes?
[DENDE]
I, uh. Uh.
[MOORI]
I'm disappointed in you, Dende.
[NAMEKS laughing]
[MOORI] You shouldn't
have given up so easily!
I was only testing you, my son!
Of course, you
can use the balls.
Sometimes, a guardian
must follow his heart
instead of the rules!
Ha. Lord Kais, forgive me, Sirs!
I really just couldn't resist.
Please, name your wishes.
[clears throat]
Dende, do the honors!
Gladly! Thank you!
[DENDE]
Vegeta! Vegeta, it's me, Dende!
We're on Namek right now,
and we have all seven
of the Dragon Balls!
We just need to know
what your wishes are.
[VEGETA]
Got it!
Now, listen carefully, Dende!
This is very important!
[DENDE]
Ready when you are!
I have two wishes
I want to make.
First, I want the planet
Earth to be restored
to its original state.
And second, I want all of
the people who were killed
since the morning of the
World Martial Arts Tournament
to be brought back to life!
Do you understand?
[VEGETA] Did you get that,
Dende? Those are my two wishes!
Uhh! Yes! I understand!
Should I make the wishes now?
[VEGETA]
Yes, right now!
[DENDE]
I-I'm sorry...
Dende! I'm putting my
faith in Vegeta's plan,
and I'd like for you
to do the same, okay?
[DENDE]
Of course, Goku!
What would you like the
third wish to be, Vegeta?
Only those two wishes matter
to me, so do what you please.
[GOKU]
Hey, just out of curiosity,
why didn't you ask the Dragon
to bring all of the people
who were killed
by Buu back to life?
Wouldn't that be easier?
Ha. No thanks! That would mean
Babidi would be revived,
and I never want to
see that little imp again!
Also, that wish wouldn't
restore all the innocent lives
I destroyed at the stadium.
I see! Wow! I'm impressed.
You really thought
this thing through.
[gasps]
No! I almost forgot! Porunga!
He only has the power to
bring one person
back to life, per wish!
Mm! You're kidding me!
That's right! He's
different than Shenron!
[DENDE]
This is awful!
We didn't give
Porunga that ability
because Nameks don't believe
in wishing people back to life.
[MOORI laughs]
As Earthlings say: Chill out!
After that Freiza debacle,
we restyled the Dragon Balls
and increased Porunga's power.
You mean, he can grant the wish?
Ah, yes he can.
Oh, sure, just great.
So much for the natural
evolution of the Universe!
[BUU screams]
[DENDE] Vegeta! Seems I was
wrong, everything's a go!
Thank goodness!
Please, proceed now!
[DENDE]
Right! We're on it!
[MOORI]
Allow me, I'll give it a whirl.
Arise, Porunga!
[OLD KAI, KABITO KAI gasp]
[PORUNGA]
Why have you awakened me?
[gasping]
It wasn't me!
[MOORI thinking]
What a magnificent sight.
[DENDE]
Porunga!
[PORUNGA growls]
Wow! He's huge! Amazing.
Why have you summoned me?
Name you first wish.
and I will grant it!
Ah, well, Mr. Guardian of Earth.
Go ahead! Get your planet back.
[gasps]
All right, Earth.
This time I'll keep you free
from harm, or I'll die trying!
I can't hear you!
[speaking Namekian]
[PORUNGA growls]
That is not an easy wish!
Okay, it shall be done.
Look! The Earth!
It's as good as new!
[laughing]
[PORUNGA] The Earth has been
restored to it's rightful place!
What is your next wish?
Uh...
Well this one's gonna
be hard to translate.
[speaking Namekian]
I don't understand!
Oh, please use your power
to restore the lives of
all those who died on Earth
since the wizard
Babidi arrived there,
except for the most evil ones!
[PORUNGA] Do you realize
what you're asking of me?
[gasps]
[DENDE]
Yes, I do!
[roars]
[PORUNGA] What you ask will take
some time, but it shall be done.
[gasps] Thank you!
Oh! Good heavens! Is such
a thing even possible?
[MR. SATAN groans]
Darn it! I said let go of him!
[barks, growls]
[MR. SATAN, BUU grunting]
Let go of him or I'll
rip your stinkin' head off,
you bug pink pretzel!
[MR. SATAN groans]
Aahh! Stop!
[groans]
[laughing]
[panting]
[BUU screams]
[BUU groaning]
Shoot, Kakarot, check
it out! Do you feel that?
Yeah, the good Buu is
losing energy, and fast.
He won't last! We're
running out of time!
Blast it! Ah! What's
taking them so long?
Dende! Hurry it up, we haven't
got all day, you know!
[OLD KAI] Yeah, yeah, we
hear you, you hot head.
What are you griping about?
Porunga's doing all the work!
[OLD KAI gasps]
[PORUNGA]
Your wish has been granted!
The people of Earth have
been restored to their home!
[laughs]
Vegeta! We did it! All the
people are back, they're alive!
Superb!
Hey! So what's next,
what's the plan? Huh?
[gasps]
Your halo, it's gone!
You're alive again!
You lucky dog!
Guess what else?!
The evil people
weren't wished back.
Verdict's in, you're a good guy!
Huh?!
What the heck! I'm
alive! I'll be darned!
Yep, we're alive all right.
Look, same old traffic jam.
[MAN 2]
We're alive!
[MAN 3]
Woo, hoo! Hallelujah!
[MAN 4]
All right! Yeah!
[GIRL]
Yes, Mommy! We're saved!
[TRUNKS]
Hey! Where are we?
[GOTEN]
I think we're back on Earth!
[TRUNKS]
That means we're alive!
[PICCOLO]
He's right, our halos are gone.
[TRUNKS]
Whoa...
[KRILLIN]
Uh. Am I going crazy,
or are we really back
on Kami's Lookout?
[OOLONG] Whatd'ya mean?
You've always been crazy!
[BULMA gasps]
[VIDEL] Maybe so, but
we really are back!
We really are on top of
Kami's Lookout, aren't we?
[screams]
[GOKU]
Ah-ha! That's it! The plan!
I know! I'll bet you're
going to have
Gohan, Goten, and Trunks fight!
Aren't you?
[VEGETA]
Wrong!
[GOKU]
Uh?!
[BUU screaming]
[KID BUU laughs]
Let's do it! Now, it's time!
It's time? Time for what?
The Spirit Bomb.
That's your big idea?
A spirit bomb?!
[laughing]
[NARRATOR] As the good Majin
Buu takes his last stand
against his evil counterpart,
Vegeta prepares to implement
the final phase of his plan!
But can a Spirit Bomb
really save the day?
[GOKU]
A spirit bomb. Yeah right.
[NARRATOR]
Goku's not so sure!
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!