[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
there's a first time
for everything,
and it was time
for Gohan's first date!
[ANGELA] Hey! What's up?!
Thanks for coming!
You're so sweet! So, what are
we going to do today?!
Well, I've never
been on a date before.
Is there something...
Hey! What about a movie?!
I love movies!
[GOHAN] Yeah, sure.
A movie sounds fun.
[ANGELA] Great!
It's settled then! Let's go!
[NARRATOR] But when
an ordinary day in the city
turned into a nightmare
for a group of citizens
who were trapped
on a burning skyscraper,
Gohan had no choice but
to leave his date behind!
[ANGELA] Gohan! Wait for me!
[NARRATOR]
The blaze was out of control.
The building had become
a treaterous inferno.
There was little hope
for the citizens
who were still trapped up above.
But the brave Videl
was determined
to buy them some time,
only to find that she, too,
had become a victim
of the terrible fire.
But wait!
[GOHAN]
Excuse me, Miss!
[NARRATOR]
It was the Great Saiyaman!
And he was ready for action!
[GOHAN] Thank you!
[GOHAN]
Stand back, everyone!
[NARRATOR]
With little time to spare,
the water swept through
the fiery building,
extinguishing the hungry
blaze one level at a time!
[NARRATOR] The crowd below
went wild, as tragedy had been
turned into triumph,
right before their very eyes!
There's a new superhero in town
and his name is
the Great Saiyaman!
[NARRATOR] After the fire
was out, Gohan put it into
stealth mode as he
tried to rejoin his date
as inconspicuously as possible!
[VIDEL]
Where are you going, Gohan?!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
So what's the rush? Huh?!
Rush? I wasn't rushing!
[laughs nervously]
Gohan, you're hiding
something!
Huh? What d'ya mean?
Hiding what?!
[NARRATOR] Hiding the fact that
you are the Great Saiyaman!
But how much longer
can you keep this up?
[GOHAN]
Goodbye, Mom!
[CHICHI] Bye, Gohan!
Have a nice day at school!
[GOHAN]
I will!
[GOHAN thinking]
Wow! I'm actually on time!
[GOTEN]
Gohan!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
Can I come?
I wanna see your school!
[GOHAN] You'd better not!
I think you'd attract
too much attention
on that thing!
Yeah! I-I guess
you're right about that!
[GOTEN]
See you later!
[GOHAN]
Bye! Have fun today!
I will! Bye!
Unbelievable! I actually
have a little time to spare.
Maybe I should go get
some breakfast or something.
Huh? I wonder who that is.
It's Saiyaman.
Oh, great! It's Videl!
I can't land here now!
Darn it! There goes
my breakfast!
Hm.
I've got you now!
Man, what's up
with this crazy girl?!
I'm not a bad guy!
What's she doing?!
[WOMAN 1]
Huh? Oh! Oh, my goodness!
[MAN 1]
Wow!
[WOMAN 2] What in
the world's going on?
[GOHAN]
Huh?!
Today's the day
I unmask that goober!
[WOMAN 3]
Huh?!
[MAN 2]
Good gravy!
[GOHAN thinking]
Hm! I know!
[VIDEL]
Aaah!
[VIDEL thinking] Oh, man!
Whoa! Now where is he?!
Whew! Man!
I don't know why she's so
bent on discovering who I am.
No one else bothers me.
This could get to be
a real nuisance! Huh?!
[laughs]
Good morning!
Hi there! I believe
we met somewhere.
Yes, I'm sure of it!
[VIDEL] How 'bout
I help you to see better
by taking that
bucket off your head?!
Enough of this nonsense.
Tell me who you are.
[GOHAN] Hm?! All right.
I guess I can trust you.
You seem like a good person.
But please don't ever repeat
what you're about to hear.
[GOHAN]
I am the...
Great Saiyaman!
You're such a jerk!
Whatd'ya mean?
You asked me who I was!
I want to know your
real name, you nut case.
And where you're from,
and where you get your power.
And if you don't tell me,
I'll find out for myself!
[GOHAN thinking]
I've never met a girl
who was this pushy before!
She reminds me of my mother!
You'd better go
or you'll be late!
Not me! I'm fine!
I have a pretty good
idea who you really are!
You think you're
so clever hiding under that--
[BOTH]
Huh?!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Nothing...
[VIDEL]
Huh?!
What do you mean nothing?!
You're stealing my jet-copter!
[GOHAN] Not stealing!
Just relocating!
I'll see you in a little while!
[GOHAN thinking]
Gohan, you idiot!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
[VIDEL]
That... guy!
That fool has no idea
who he's messing with!
[school bell chimes]
I'm sorry I'm late, sir.
Ah! Hello, Videl! Good morning!
We know that your
community service sometimes
takes precedence
over your school work.
[Please, take a seat
and join the class.
[VIDEL]
Yes, sir.
[yelps]
Hey, girl! Were you
up early fighting crime?
Not really! Just late!
[ERASA whispering] Don't worry.
You haven't missed anything.
It's been boring!
Hey, it strikes me
as a funny coincidence
that you and Gohan
were both late this morning.
What? Gohan was late?
So, what's going on?
What? I overslept! That's all!
[chuckles]
[GOHAN]
You're too much, Sharpner!
There's nothing going on
between us! Is there, Videl?
[VIDEL]
Of course not!
[laughs]
[VIDEL thinking] But I still
think he's hiding something.
[REPORTER] Winning the
hearts of people everywhere
is the Great Saiyaman--
who is seen here flying
over downtown yesterday!
Log on to our website
and let us know
how you feel
about this new hero!
Fools! They call
that runt a hero?!
I could break that little
scrawny, runt in two
like a soggy toothpick!
[laughs]
[class tune chimes]
[STUDENTS talking]
[police sirens blaring]
--[GOHAN] Huh?
--[GIRL] Wow!
Hey, pigs!
Catch us if you can!
[PASSENGER chuckles]
[WOMAN screams]
Oh my gosh!
Right on!
You sure know how to
take care of
those stupid cops, Jimbo!
Yeah! I think that moving the
boss' operation to this city
is going to be
easier than we thought!
[SLIMJIM] Yeah! If all
the cops are this stupid,
it'll be a breeze!
[BOTH laugh]
[GOHAN]
That was a dangerous stunt
you guys pulled back there!
Oh? Why, thank you!
[JIMBO] But it's not nearly
as dangerous as the stunt
that you're pulling right now!
[SLIMJIM]
Yeah!
We're gonna make
an example of you!
So all the other punks
know not to smart off
to the Red Shark Gang!
[SLIMJIM]
Let him have it, Jimbo!
Huh? Gohan!
Violence isn't the answer, sir!
Oh, yeah?!
Aah!
You missed me! Huh?
Hey, Videl! Huh?
[JIMBO grunts]
Ah!
[VIDEL]
You jerk!
[JIMBO groans]
[VIDEL grunts]
[SLIMJIM]
Jimbo! Uhh!
What happened?!
She's just a kid!
You haven't seen
the last of us, you punk!
[VIDEL]
Yeah.
Oh, Gohan!
I don't even want to look!
How bad is it?!
[SLIMJIM]
You're going to get it, kid!
Well, I think I'll be okay!
Huh?! He pounded you
in the face and...
you don't even have a scratch!
I don't?!
Not even a black eye?!
Man! How lucky can you get?!
[chuckles]
Oh, it's my fault! You're
not gonna believe this,
but I didn't jump in
to help you because
I thought you would be okay,
because I honestly believed
that you were
the Great Saiyaman!
Me?! No way!
[VIDEL] I was convinced of it
until I saw you fight. Uh!
Please don't take on
any more criminals, Gohan.
Sorry, but you don't
have what it takes.
But you sure know how to
take a punch in the face!
Gee! Thanks!
[GOHAN thinking]
Whew! Wow!
I might have to get punched
in the face more often!
Guess what?
That girl back there--
think that was Mr. Satan's kid.
We might have to get the boss
to take care of her as well!
I can handle
that little punk!
She just caught me
off guard! Shoot!
It's the skinny kid
that's unusual! Yeah!
I think I busted
my hand on his face!
What?!
No joke! It felt like I was
hitting a wall of solid steel!
[LADY TEACHER] All right,
class, open your books
to page seventy-three.
Please read the poem in silence
and then we'll read it
together and discuss it!
[ERASA] So he comes up
to me and he says,
"Erasa, I love you!"
Can you believe it?!
I mean, I hardly
even know the guy!
[beeping]
[VIDEL]
Oops! Just a second, Erasa!
Yes. This is Videl!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
[MALE VOICE] Videl, a gang
called the Red Shark Gang
has taken the Mayor hostage and
is holding him at knife-point!
[VIDEL] Huh? Hold on!
I'll be right there!
[CAPTAIN] All right,
I want Stealth Team One
to cover the roof!
And Stealth Team Two
to cover the rear entrance!
[SERGEANT]
Yes, sir!
[JIMBO] Look! All we want is for
Mr. Satan to get over here!
When he shows up,
you can have fatty back!
Please! I don't understand!
What do you want
with Mr. Satan?
Hey, it's no big deal.
My boss just wants to
challenge him to a fight!
What?! He can't win!
[JIMBO chuckles]
[BOSS] What does a plump,
little cornish-hen like you
know about winning
a fight anyway?!
You people worship
that fraud because
you think he's strong!
I'll show you what strength is!
Then I'll be your hero!
Heh! What a role model!
I wish I had someone
like you to look up to
when I was a kid!
Thanks, SlimJim!
We give you key
to city for that!
Aren't we, Mr. Mayor?!
[BOSS]
Yes, I thought so!
Hey, Coppers! Here's a
little love letter from
the Red Shark Gang for
not bringing Mr. Satan yet!
[COPS yell]
What's the word, G?
Sir, he doesn't
appear to be home!
We've tried knockin'
on the door and callin'!
[phone ringing]
[MR. SATAN] Where are those
guys when you need them?!
The one's that
helped me to beat Cell!
I could use a couple of
good assistants like that!
I can't respond to
every lunatic that wants
to challenge me!
It's too dangerous!
Just look at those thugs,
loaded up with
every kind of
firearm imaginable!
And I'm supposed to
go out and face that?!
This is your last chance!
Bring Mr. Satan here
or the Mayor dies!
Please excuse me, madam!
[LADY TEACHER]
Mm? Yes, of course!
Be careful, Videl!
[GOHAN]
Uh-- Pardon me, ma'am!
[LADY TEACHER]
Huh?
Hi! Sorry! Can I be excused
to use the bathroom?!
[SHARPNER]
Hmph. Yeah, right!
No, sir! Not this time, Gohan!
You have a bad habit
of not coming back to class!
[GOHAN]
Wha...?
You heard me!
Now please take a seat
and finish the reading
for discussion!
You're gonna have to hold it!
[GOHAN]
Uh--
[SHARPNER chuckles]
[MAYOR grunting]
[RED]
Boss, look! Above us!
[BOSS] Huh?! Excellent!
Get ready for action, boys!
[RED, JIMBO, and SLIMJIM laugh]
[RED]
This is gonna be great!
[VIDEL grunts] All right,
you crooks! Let him go!
You can still get off easy!
Boss! That's Mr. Satan's girl!
The one I told you about!
Oh! Well, well, well!
So you're the tough girl,
Mr. Satan's daughter!
Where's your father?!
What kind of hero
would send his little girl
to fight for him?!
[VIDEL] Look, mister,
my father didn't send me here!
I'm like a maid!
I go wherever the filth is
and I clean it up!
My father's a busy man!
If you wanna challenge him,
you're gonna have to
get through me first!
You?!
No! No, Videl!
This man's too strong!
I could never forgive myself
if something happened!
Look! I came here
to fight your father
but if I have to
teach you a lesson first
to get him out here,
then, so be it!
All right!
Let's get this over with!
Now! Little big-girl!
Time to learn not to mess
with the Red Shark Gang!
Well, whenever you feel lucky!
[VIDEL]
Hmm!
[BOSS grunts]
Sharks are vicious,
but they're not much on brains!
[BOSS laughs] And you're
supposed to be some genius?!
Don't make me laugh!
[GOHAN thinking] Whoever this
guy is, he's alot stronger
than the thugs
we faced the other day!
I've got to get over there
before it's too late!
[LADY TEACHER]
Thee in thy larger,
saner brood of female, male!
Thee in thy athletes,
moral, spiritual;
South North, West, East!
Thee and thy moral
wealth and civilization.
Until which thy proudest...
[GOHAN]
Huh...
Thee in thy all supplying,
all-enclosing worship--
Thee in no single bible,
savior merely,
Thy saviors, countless,
latent within thyself,
equal to any, divine as any.
These! These in thee, certain
to come today, as I do prophesy!
Well, Mr. Whitman
was certainly very--
Earthquake!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
[LADY TEACHER] Children!
Children! Please! Don't panic!
Everyone get on the floor
and cover your necks
with your hands!
[GOHAN thinking]
Wow! All right!
[GOHAN]
The Great Saiyaman!
[BOSS, VIDEL grunting]
Whoa! You're going
to pay for that one!
[RED, SLIMJIM, and JIMBO laugh]
Aaah!
Now we're doomed!
Hey, you! Back off!
[BOSS]
Huh?
You back off, chump!
--[GOHAN] Hmph!
--[RED] Huh?
[GOHAN]
Mister, you and your men better
get out of this city
while you still can!
[BOSS]
Who are you?
Who am I?!
Saiyaman!
Hey! Go home!
Whoa! Oh, hi there!
Fancy meeting you again!
[VIDEL] Look! No one
asked you to come here!
Stop interfering
in my business, jerk!
Huh?
You heard me!
I can handle this!
But I just, uh...
[VIDEL]
You just wanna get in my way!
I can handle this on my own!
This character's
a trouble maker!
[VIDEL]
Now leave! Get outta here!
[GOHAN] If this is
about earlier this morning,
I-I'm sorry...
I didn't mean to...
Enough! I cannot
take it anymore!
Boys, shut this guy up for good!
[RED, SLIMJIM, JIMBO,
THUG 1, and THUG 2] Right!
[GOHAN]
Huh?!
Aaah!
[THUG 1]
Huh?
[GOHAN grunts]
[THUG 1 groans]
[SLIMJIM, THUG 1 groan]
Are you okay there, sir?!
Yes! Thanks to you!
[MAYOR screams]
[GOHAN] Huh?
[THUG 2]
Huh?
[GOHAN] Here! I think
this belongs to you!
[GOHAN] Sir, I wouldn't use
weapons like that if I were you!
You could get hurt!
Oh...
[GOHAN]
Hm!
[BOSS]
Now I've got you!
Huh?!
Let go of her!
[VIDEL grunts]
[BOSS groans]
[GOHAN gasps]
[VIDEL grunts]
[VIDEL]
Hm!
[GOHAN thinking]
What a girl! She decked him!
She really didn't need
my help afterall! Amazing!
[REPORTER]
Mr. Mayor! Please comment!
Who are the Red Shark Gang?
[MAYOR] Just some thugs
who met their match
in Videl and Saiyaman!
[GOHAN]
Goodbye, Miss Videl!
[VIDEL]
Hey, wait!
Thank you!
Sure! No prob!
Hey, this doesn't mean
that I've given up
trying to find out
who you really are!
I'm gonna unmask you,
Mr. Saiyaman!
[GOHAN laughs nervously]
Whatever you say! See ya later!
[ERASA]
All right, Videl, spill it!
What's going on between
you and you-know-who?!
What are you talking about?!
You mean Gohan?!
That's exactly who I mean!
He disappeared from
Miss Beakman's class
right after you left!
She wouldn't let him leave,
and then the earthquake hit
and he was gone!
You're kidding!
[ERASA]
No!
Darn him! Now where'd he go?!
I thought he was
walking behind us!
[ERASA]
He was...
[SHARPNER] Look you two!
When a geek disappears,
you're not supposed
to worry about it!
It's a good thing!
[VIDEL]
Gohan's not a geek!
He's a heck of alot cooler
than you, Sharpner!
[SHARPNER]
What?!
[VIDEL]
You heard me!
[ERASA]
Yeah! And he's cuter, too!
[SHARPNER] Yeah, if you
like your men scrawny and weak!
[ERASA] Videl doesn't
need a strong man!
She can kick your butt
all by herself!
[SHARPNER]
No she can't!
[ERASA]
Yes, she can!
[VIDEL]
Yes, I can!
[SHARPNER]
Whatever.