[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the unknown soldier
efficiently disposed
of the treacherous Frieza
and his diabolical
father, King Cold!
[NARRATOR] Keeping his
identity a secret,
the stranger proceeded to
predict the time and place
of Goku's return to Earth,
down to the second.
[BULMA] Wait for me!
[NARRATOR] And when
a spacecraft landed
right where the
stranger had predicted,
it looked like the star-voyaging
hero had finally returned.
[GOHAN gasps]
Uh... Hey, guys!
[cheering, whooping]
What took you so long, Dad?
Where did he get that outfit?
How did you guys know
that I was coming?
The identity of the mystery
man is unveiled, today!
Oh, Goku! Hey!
--What's up?
--Hi, Daddy!
Check him out!
You're the man!
[GOKU] Hi, you guys!
How in the world did you
know I was going to be here?
This guy told us!
He's a mystery man!
I think he might
be a fan of yours.
He knows all about you, Daddy!
Huh?
But how?
[ALL] Huh?
[BULMA] He knew the exact time
and place of your arrival, Goku!
[GOKU] That's impossible!
We've never even met!
Well, that's what he said.
Then he must have been tracking
your ship in outer space.
Really? I don't know...
Frieza tried to do that.
But I could sense his energy
level as he passed me.
He sure was in a hurry
to beat me home.
But my gosh! What in the world
happened here, you guys?
Who defeated Frieza?
You, Piccolo?
Or was it you, Vegeta?
Neither of us did. It was
this guy. He did it with ease.
[GOKU] Huh...?
He turned into a Super Saiyan
and picked him apart.
What? A Super Saiyan?
I can't believe it!
That's outstanding!
Can you imagine? A Super
Saiyan at his age! Fantastic!
Hey! Aren't you
forgetting something?!
You, your son, and I are
the only Saiyans still alive!
Hm.. Well, if he says
he's a Super Saiyan,
then that's good enough for me.
Oh, honestly, Goku!
You take things way
too lightly sometimes!
[GOKU] No, I don't.
Goku!
Hm?
[BOY] Could I have
a word with you?
With me?
[BOY] Yes. Just the two of us.
[ALL] Huh?
All right, then.
[YAMCHA] Hey! What exactly
is this guy trying to say?
[GOKU] It's okay, guys!
I'll be right back.
Hmph!
[TRUNKS] Thanks, man.
Hey, no problem! But shoot!
I should be thanking you
for beating Frieza!
I had a chance to finish him,
but I was only fooling myself,
thinking that he might change.
Not him.
He was out of control and you
were supposed to stop him.
But when he landed
and you weren't around,
I had to step in. I didn't
think you would make it.
Yeah, his ship was a
lot faster than mine
and he gained two hours on me!
I knew he was going to
hurt the people here!
I was about to make my move!
But then you came along!
And just how were you
going to make a move
when you were two
hours away in space?
Well, thanks to a
technique I learned,
I could have been
there in seconds!
Are you serious?
Yeah! It's called
Instant Transmission!
You mean time travel?!
No, you dematerialize and
travel as a mass of light!
You'd be surprised how
much ground you can cover
going one hundred and eighty
six thousand miles per second!
[BOY] No kidding? I had no
idea that you had that ability!
[GOKU] Yeah, the people
on Yardrat taught it to me!
They weren't very strong,
but they knew some
amazing techniques!
And I think they liked me
because I could eat as much
as they could!
[BOY] Man! What a bummer!
Huh...?
If I had known that you didn't
need my help with Frieza,
I could have waited and come
to you while you were alone
and avoided the risk of
meeting all the others!
The risk? What d'ya mean?
[BOY] Okay, I don't mind
answering that question.
But first let me
ask you something:
Can you transform into
a Super Saiyan at will?
[GOKU] Well, at first
I wasn't able to.
It happened spontaneously.
But now I can control it.
Alright then. Can you
show me right now?
Huh?
Please, Goku.
[BULMA] I really like Goku's
new outfit! It's cool!
[KRILLIN] I wonder what
they're talking about?
[GOHAN] Yeah, they
look pretty serious.
Okay!
[GOKU growls]
[gasping]
What's going on, guys?! Goku
has blonde hair! How wild!
He just transformed
into a Super Saiyan!
How can he generate
that much power?!
I know, it's mind boggling!
Goku's on fire!
[VEGETA growls]
Are you satisfied?
[BOY] Yes! I am!
Man, how awesome!
I'd forgotten what it feels like
looking from the outside in!
So, what's next, friend?
Now we'll both be Super Saiyans!
[GOKU gasps]
Huh?!
Man, look at those two!
Hard core!
What's that guy up to?
[VEGETA growls]
We're exactly the same!
Let's find out!
Huh?
[yelling]
[gasping]
Hm! Why didn't you
try to avoid it?
I searched your feelings,
so I knew that you would stop.
Yes, I see!
Well, this time I'm not
going to stop! Got it?
[GOKU] As you wish.
[yelling]
[shouting,
clanging]
Hmph!
Awesome! Everything
I've heard is true!
You're good-- No, you're great!
Man, those same moves turned
Frieza into cold cuts.
Yeah, well your heart
just wasn't in it this time.
I feel like I can
trust you, Goku.
I had to know that for sure.
Man! Goku!
Yeah! He's spectacular!
[TIEN] No doubt!
Blast you, Kakarot!
[BOY] Sorry about
all of the secrecy,
but I really need your word that
you won't tell anybody else
what I'm about to say.
Well, I've never had a
problem keeping secrets.
But sure, you have my word.
Thank you, my name is Trunks.
This is going to
sound really strange.
But I'm not from this time, I
traveled here in a time machine,
twenty years from the future.
Really? From the future?
That's incredible!
Yes, Vegeta was right.
Only he, yourself, and
Gohan have Saiyan blood!
And I got mine from him.
He's my father.
What?! Your kidding!
Wow! You're absolutely sure
that Vegeta's your father?!
Yes, I'm half Saiyan,
half Earthling!
[GOKU] You're serious!
Vegeta's son. My gosh!
[GOKU] Yes, yes, I can see
the resemblance! Wow...
[TRUNKS] I will be born
two years from now.
[GOKU] Ha, ha, ha! No kidding!
Vegeta's going to be a daddy!
That's incredible! Man,
who would have ever thought?!
Goku! I didn't come
here to tell you that.
I have to talk to
you about something.
In three years, on the
morning of May 12th at 10AM,
a horribly destructive
duo will show up
on an island nine miles
southwest of South City!
They have dreadful power,
even by our standards!
They're monsters, Goku!
That's the best way I know to
describe them: they're monsters!
Once this pair surfaces,
the Earth and everything you
know will be gone for good.
What's the deal?
Are they aliens?
No. They're both androids
created right here on Earth.
Their creator is Gero!
Doctor Gero,
the mastermind responsible
for the old Red Ribbon Army.
Do you remember?
Yeah! I defeated them!
[BULMA] Man, for two guys
who don't know each other,
they sure do have
a lot to talk about!
But, hey! Talking's not bad.
It's a lot better than fighting.
Uhh...
At least he doesn't have
his sword out anymore.
[KRILLIN] Yeah, and your dad
put his finger away, too.
No way! Same guy? Wow!
[TRUNKS] That's him.
But how? He lived?
[TRUNKS] Thanks to you!
[GOKU groans]
[TRUNKS] Yes! That's one
battle that you're going to wish
you fought to the very end.
Look, I'm sorry
to say that, Goku.
I know you're a good person.
But letting Doctor Gero
escape was a mistake
that will come back to haunt
you and everyone you know.
He's probably working on
those monsters as we speak.
I'm still not sure where
his laboratory is...
If I knew, I'd be paying
him a visit, instead of you.
It's hard to describe
these creatures, Goku!
They're unlike anyone
you've ever faced.
Nothing even comes close
to rivaling the technology
that gave them birth.
It's mind boggling
how strong they are.
What's his plan?
What's Doctor Gero trying
to accomplish with them?
No one really knows.
The moment those things were
able to think for themselves,
they rebelled.
And they've had
their own twisted,
merciless agenda
ever since then...
There's no rhyme or
reason to what they do.
They're machines of
destruction! Man-eaters!
Their first act after being born
was to turn on their own
creator, Doctor Gero himself!
[DR. GERO] No!
What are you doing?!
You can't harm me! I made you!
[DR. GERO] Nooo!
These androids are ruthless!
They delight in causing
pain and chaos!
[TRUNKS] Living on
Earth in my time
is like living in a nightmare!
Always running and hiding
and looking for a way out!
[GOKU] Hm, man... Gosh.
You defeated Frieza
in a flash, and yet,
from what you're saying,
these androids are even
stronger than you.
[TRUNKS] They are! For sure!
Hunting me down is one
of their favorite hobbies.
But it's two against one!
There's not much I can do
against them except run!
What? What about
all the others?!
I mean, aren't they helping you?
They can't...
[GOKU] Huh...?
They're dead.
Three years from now, the
Earth's Special Forces
will be gone.
I'm all that's left!
I'm doing the best I can!
They're all gone!
Vegeta! Krillin! Yamcha!
Tien! Chiaotzu! Piccolo!
They're all going to lose their
lives against the androids
in a horrible battle!
There will be only
one survivor...
That's my Master and
best friend, Gohan!
He narrowly escapes
from that battle,
but then, thirteen years
later, they finally get him!
[TRUNKS growls]
That was four years
ago my time...
And as you already
know Piccolo is gone
so there's no chance of reviving
anyone with the Dragon Balls!
[YAMCHA]
Now what's the deal?
They look like somebody
just died over there!
Making the time machine also
cost us many precious lives.
So many have suffered at
the hands of those beasts!
[TRUNKS growls]
Darn them! Man! They're
just far too strong!
Wait a sec! Hey, Trunks!
What happens to me?
Do I die in the battle as well?
Uh-uh. You die before it.
Huh?
Not too long from now
you're going to catch a new
virus that attacks the heart.
You're going to die from it.
Huh?!
[TRUNKS] Sorry to be
the bearer of bad news.
It's a radical virus! You'll
start hearing about it soon.
Not even a Super Saiyan
can beat it!
[GOKU] What a bummer!
Being killed by a stupid virus!
Rrgh! What a waste! Darn it!
I want to fight those androids!
Huh?
[GOKU] I don't even get
to take a crack at them!
You mean after
everything you've heard,
you still want to fight them?
Aren't you scared
of them at all?
Well, sure, a little bit!
All challenges
are scary at first.
Maybe I could make a difference!
A guy like you probably
could! You're a true warrior!
My Mother and Gohan were
right about you, Goku!
I really can trust you!
I'm glad I came.
Huh?
Here you go.
Take this, man. For your health.
My health?
[TRUNKS] It's an antidote.
[GOKU] Hmm?
[TRUNKS] There's no cure
now for that nasty virus
you're going to get,
but in my time there is.
Take this when you get
sick and you'll be fine.
You're kidding me! Wow!
Awesome! It's purple, too!
I'll bet it's grape flavored!
I shouldn't be doing this, Goku,
because it's going
to change history.
But some history should change.
Things are pretty bad.
We're living in fear.
With no way out, it's terrible!
But you can make
a difference, Goku.
My Mother told me that you
could and now I believe her!
Your mother knows me?
Am I going to meet her,
or do I already know her now?
Now...
Oh, wow! I know your
mom, huh? That's bizarre!
Does she live by me
or something?
[TRUNKS] She's standing
right there.
[GOKU screams with laughter]
Bulma's your mother?!
[laughing continues]
[PICCOLO gasps]
That guy just pointed his
finger and Kakarot fell down!
[BULMA] I could have sworn
I heard Goku call my name.
[GOKU] Wow! Bulma and
Vegeta, huh? Unbelievable!
I thought Bulma was gonna
end up marrying Yamcha!
But, man! Vegeta?
They don't stay together long.
It's, uh, more of a
passion kind of thing...
You know how stubborn they are.
[GOKU chuckles]
[YAMCHA sneezes]
Excuse you.
Yamcha and my mother
are going to break up.
He finds someone else
and my mom...
she falls in love with my dad.
'Course, he can never admit
that he loves my mother.
No shock there.
I know them and man-o-man!
They're the feistiest
two people I know.
I don't remember my dad.
So it's really great
to get to meet him.
He's a cranky guy,
but he's impressive.
Hey, that guy's looking
over here, isn't he?
Yeah, it looks
like he's smiling.
I know it's bizarre,
but they'll find their way
to each other pretty soon.
Huh...?
But if they get wind of
it, it might not happen.
Promise you won't tell them,
Goku, or I might not be born!
Hey! Not a problem!
[TRUNKS] Well, look,
I better be off.
My mom's worried sick about me.
She needs to know that
everything went okay.
[GOKU] Yeah! Please tell
her that I send my love!
And thanks for this!
You're great!
Hey! You've helped me
in a lot of ways.
I should be thanking you.
[GOKU] Me? What did I do?
[TRUNKS] Well, I've felt
alone since Gohan died.
He was the last person that
understood me and my power.
But meeting you has
inspired me, Goku.
It's been like finding
a long, lost brother.
You take care!
You too! You're a brave
young man, Trunks!
Now that I've met you,
I'll be with you in spirit
no matter where you go.
[KRILLIN] Huh?!
[YAMCHA] Man! He didn't
even say goodbye!
[GOKU] Oh, man!
Now what? Three years!
Gosh, how am I going
to let them know?
--[GOHAN] Daddy!
--Huh?
[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku!
So what did that guy say?
[GOKU] Oh, uh, well,
nothing important really.
Huh?
That's funny. It all sounded
pretty important to me.
[GOKU gasps]
Uh, really? You heard it all?
My ears do more than just
frame my face, you know, Goku.
[BULMA] Oh, c'mon!
What's so important that
you can't tell us, Goku?
Well, I can't really say.
Alright, that's fine.
But if you won't, I will.
But gosh, you heard!
[PICCOLO] Don't worry, Goku.
I won't say anything that
would endanger your friend.
But we deserve a chance
to change our destinies!
All of us, not just him!
[BULMA] "Destinies"...?
[PICCOLO] ...And that's
the whole story.
In three years,
all of us except Gohan
are supposed to die in a
battle with the androids.
But now that we know,
maybe we can change that.
What a kook! He's cracked!
Don't you think?
I'm not so sure.
Look, believe what
you want to believe.
As for me, I want to live.
So I'm going to train.
Huh?
[PICCOLO] You can risk it,
but I'm going to be prepared.
[YAMCHA] Look! There he is!
Father! You're so
tough and proud!
Hard and cold like a rock!
But still, deep down, your
heart beats like mine does...
I know you feel! I'm your son,
and I will always love you!
I'm glad I got
to see you, Dad...
Farewell, young Mother! May the
good spirits keep you safe!
He's gone.
[PICCOLO] Yeah,
back to the future...
[BULMA} How strange.
I could have sworn he was
waving goodbye... to me...
Man, I'm going
to train, you guys.
Me too.
Yeah, I am, too.
[thinking] Another Super Saiyan!
Rrrgh! I've got to have it!
I've got to experience it!
[thinking] Gosh... Goodbye,
whoever you are...
[GOHAN] Wow! Gosh, Dad!
Do you really believe that
that guy came from the future?
[GOKU] Yes, I do,
Son! Yes, I do...
[NARRATOR] As the young Super
Saiyan named Trunks
heads down stream
in the river of time,
Goku and the others consider
the fantastic prophecies
that he left behind
On the next Dragon Ball Z!