[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta was attacked from
within by Babidi's dark magic,
and by the hatred from his past.
[GOKU]
Vegeta... You didn't...
[cackles]
How sad...
I didn't figure you were weak
enough to be controlled.
[NARRATOR] All the
bitterness, hurt and anger
that had ruled Vegeta long ago
were brought to the surface.
It conusmed him!
[NARRATOR] And put him
under Babidi's control.
In a single, devistating
instant, it was clear.
The Dark Prince had returned.
The evil that had been
surpressed in Vegeta's heart
for years was once again brought
to life by Babidi's magic.
There could be no negotiation.
Vegeta was beyond
reason, beyond logic.
Only action would prevent him
from causing any further harm.
Realizing this, Goku did the
only thing he could.
[GOKU]
Babidi!
Transport us to a place
away from people!
If you give me that,
then I will fight Vegeta!
[NARRATOR] Goku was playing
right into Babidi's hands.
But not even the protests
of the Supreme Kai
could dissuade him from
his course of action.
[NARRATOR] Left with no other
option, the Supreme Kai
and Gohan descended into
Babidi's ship in the hopes
of destroying Majin Buu
before he could be returned
to full power.
All of the energy lost by
Goku in the coming struggle
will be absorbed by
the sleeping monster,
and there's sure
to be plenty of it.
Vegeta isn't taking
this fight lightly.
[VEGETA] You see!
This is our fate. Our battle!
[NARRATOR] The Super Saiyan
showdown is about to begin.
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
[MR. SATAN]
Uh... Ah... Uh...
Hey, uh... Mister Satan?
I hope you'll understand
if we postpone
your awards ceremony...
Of course.
After all that's happened,
I think that would be
the right thing to do.
Besides, all the
TV crews have run off.
Okay, we'll reschedule
for later, then.
[MR. SATAN]
Hm.
I guess we should probably
tell the runner-up.
What do you mean?
About the delay, of course.
I think Number 18
will wanna be here
to collect her prize for
second place, don't you?
Uh-- Number 18?!
Wh-uh...
Uuuh...
What? Are you kidding?
Ha! Of course she'll
wanna be here!
She worked hard for this
honor. She deserves it!
Not many people
can stand next to me
when I put on my
Championship Belt!
[laughs]
[CHICHI]
How could he do this?
I really thought
Vegeta knew better.
I didn't think he'd ever wanna
hurt people like this again.
What kind of an
example is he setting--
[gasps]
You don't think Trunks was...
Goten was with him!
They wouldn't have
been down there...
Would they?
Vegeta, what happened to you?
[VEGETA laughs]
[yells]
[grunts]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[GOKU groaning]
--[VEGETA grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
What's this?
I thought you said we were
skipping the warm-up!
I guess I was wrong.
[GOKU, VEGETA grunt]
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU groans]
--[VEGETA grunting]
--[GOKU groaning]
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA groaning]
That's more like it!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA, GOKU panting]
[growls]
[VEGETA, GOKU yell]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[BOTH groan]
[yells]
[GOKU groaning]
[BABIDI cackles]
Good! Keep it up, Vegeta!
Hit him again, hit him again!
Oooh! Aah! Yes!
Nice shot! Very nice...
Ooh! Look, Dabura!
At this rate, Majin Buu
will be at full power
in no time!
[BABIDI cackles]
[BABIDI] The only thing
we have to do now
is decide how we're going to
exterminate the Supreme Kai.
That rat...
Yes, Master.
[cackles] Oh, what a happy day!
I haven't laughed this
much in years! [cackles]
Huh?
[SOLDIERS whimpering]
It's them, they're here!
We should get 'em, right?
It seems we have a
welcoming committee.
We don't have time
to waste on small fish.
Let's hurry!
Right!
[SOLDIER 1]
Ready, men? Attack!
[SOLDIERS]
Yeah!
[GOHAN]
Hm.
[SOLDIERS yelp, whimper]
[SOLDIERS scream]
Whew! I think that will do.
Good work, Gohan.
[door clangs]
Huh?
[SUPREME KAI] He's practically
daring us to come.
It would be a terrible shame
to disappoint him, wouldn't it?
Come, Gohan. Let's put
an end to this ordeal.
Yeah!
[DABURA]
Leave them to me, Master.
and I will have the Kai
groveling at your feet
before he dies.
I could just sing!
[DABURA, BABIDI cackle]
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA groans]
[GOKU grunts]
Huh?
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[gasps]
You're not going to win.
Not this time!
[yells]
[GOKU yells]
[GOTEN grunting]
Huh?
What are you doing, Goten?!
If you don't hurry,
we're gonna to miss
seeing that Buu monster!
I know, but--
[TRUNKS]
But what? What is it with you?!
[GOTEN]
I have to go to the bathroom!
[TRUNKS] We're gonna
miss all the cool stuff!
Darn it! Can't you
just hold it in?
No! I can't!
I haven't gone since
before we played
in the tournament this morning.
It's gonna come out!
I swear, you're such
a baby sometimes!
There. See down there?
Go take care of your business!
And hurry!
[GOTEN]
'Kay!
[zips]
--[water trickles]
--[sighs]
Trunks! What are you doing?
Eh heh! "When you gotta go"...
[BOTH sigh]
[TRUNKS]
He, he! Hey, watch this.
I can write my name!
[GOTEN]
Oh yeah? I can too!
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
T... R... U-
[TRUNKS]
Hey, write your own name, dummy!
[GOTEN] Oh yeah!
G... O... T...
[BOTH]
Huh?
[GOTEN, TRUNKS scream]
Phew. That was close.
Told you not to stop.
Now we'd better hurry!
[GOTEN]
Mm!
[TRUNKS]
Stupid.
Don't know why I'm surprised.
He has been training for the
last seven years straight.
Vegeta...
[yells]
[GOKU yells]
[laughs]
[grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
What's the matter?
Not winning as easily
as you thought?
I never said it would be easy.
You won't be winning at all!
What, clown?
Are you feeling angry?
Humiliated? Is that it?
[GOKU groans]
[VEGETA] Fool! You don't
know what humiliation is!
Don't worry. I will teach you
its bitter taste, just as you...
...have taught me!
Me! A warrior elite!
In my fingertips I hold the
power to destroy entire worlds!
I am a Saiyan
of royal blood,
the last of my kind,
and on my shoulders rests
the glory of an
extinct warrior race.
Whole civilizations
once trembled
at the sound of my name.
But you didn't,
did you Kakarot?
And at your hands,
your common hands,
my honor and my pride,
the foundations upon which
I have always stood,
began to crumble at my feet.
It was at your hands
that I suffered my first
great humiliation, toppled
by a piece of low-level trash.
[VEGETA] Imagine my added
shame when it was you,
and not me, who avenged our
people by defeating Frieza.
You, who were
the first to achieve
the pinnacle of our race,
the first in 1,000 years to take
a place among the Super Saiyans
of legend, a place that
I had been raised
to believe was
my royal birthright!
[VEGETA] And imagine
the disgrace I suffered
when the strength I had
worked my whole life
to acquire was surpassed
by a mere child!
Your half-breed son
succeeded where I,
the prince of all
Saiyans had failed!
It is time to take
back what is mine!
I will not live my
life as your second!
That time is over...
Every breath you take
is an assault to my honor.
But no more, Kakarot.
By my hands,
you will be cut down,
inch by inch,
the way you have
cut down my pride!
[GOKU grunting]
[yelling]
What?
[screams]
[GOKU yells]
[VEGETA groans]
[yells]
[VEGETA groaning]
[GOKU thinking] Focus...
I know you're here Vegeta...
I'll sense where
you're hiding...
[rock clatters]
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
I'm here, fool!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU yells]
[VEGETA yelps]
--[GOKU] Ka-me-ha-me...
--[VEGETA] Gallic...
--Ha!
--Gun!
[GOHAN, SUPREME KAI gasp]
[SUPREME KAI]
This is it, Gohan.
This is what we're here to find.
And Majin Buu's inside?
Yes. We must act quickly.
I doubt Babidi and Dabura will
leave it unguarded for long.
If we combine our powers,
we may still have a
chance to destroy it.
[GOHAN thinking]
It's terrible...
I've never sensed
anything like this.
So cold, and empty...
--[BABIDI] Welcome, friends!
--Huh?
[BABIDI]
I'm glad you could join us!
Especially you, Supreme Kai.
We've come to stop you, Babidi.
Like you did my father?
I will not let you
resurrect Majin Buu.
That's too bad.
I'm sure Dabura
won't like that one bit.
He was so looking forward
to meeting Buu today,
and you know... I really
hate to see him upset.
Let's hurry, Gohan...
We haven't much time.
Every second we allow
to pass brings Majin Buu
one step closer to
his full power.
Right!
I will take care
of Babidi myself.
[yells]
[NARRATOR] The battle
between Goku and Vegeta
rages on with
explosive intensity!
Nothing less than victory will
satisfy these proud Saiyans,
but this is one contest that
may be impossible to win,
for with every blow
they land, they send more
of their energy to the
sleeping Majin Buu...
Can Gohan and the
Supreme Kai put a stop
to Babidi and his evil plans
before it's too late?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!