[MAN yells]
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the Androids have arrived!
And these merciless machines
are unleashing their fury
upon a city of
unsuspecting citizens.
Their diabolical deeds locking
this bustling metropolis
in a stranglehold of terror.
[MAN D rasps]
[NARRATOR]
Yamcha's on the look out,
and he's more than ready
to spring into action
against these terrible
new enemies.
But watch out, Yamcha!
Because it looks
like the Androids
have their evil eyes set on you!
[ANDROID 20] Excellent.
[YAMCHA] Huh?
You two better
be careful!
There's a couple of
Androids on the loose
and they mean business!
We are they.
I found them!
[NARRATOR]
Try as he might,
Yamcha is no match for the
Androids' awesome power!
And all of his struggles
can do nothing
to prevent even greater
destruction from raining down!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[NARRATOR] Now, as the city
crumbles around him,
separated from his friends,
Yamcha finds himself staring
into the face of evil!
[bones crunching]
[NARRATOR] Can anything free him
from the Android's
sinister grasp?
Will Goku and the others arrive
to help their friend in time?
Find out on today's
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[GOKU] Huh...?
Hmm?!
Someone's power
level is draining!
But who's?!
I think that's...
I think that's Yamcha!
I've got to hurry!
[TIEN gasps]
[TIEN growls]
[GOKU] Oh no...
Yamcha!
[GOKU growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[TIEN growls]
[GOKU growls]
[gasping]
Krillin, listen!
There's still a
chance to save him!
Take him back to Bulma and give
him one of the Senzu Beans.
Go now, as fast as you can!
I'm on it!
[GOKU growls]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN growls]
[GOKU] I'm counting
on you, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Right!
So these are the
big, bad androids.
Kind of funny-looking
if you ask me.
Hmm?
Well now.
I find it surprising that you
should know we are androids.
Of course...
I find it even more
surprising that all of you
should have anticipated
our arrival on this island.
[ANDROID 20] Tell me,
how did you know we would come?
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO] If you're so tough,
why don't you try to make us?
Very well.
[ALL yell]
There's way too many
innocent people around here.
We've got to lead these
two out of the city!
--[ANDROID 20] Yes.
--[GOKU] Huh?!
It is too crowded here.
I agree.
Many people could
get in our way.
I will see to it
that they do not.
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU &amp; TIEN gasp]
[GOKU] Nooooo!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[TIEN gasps]
[TIEN whimpers]
[YAMCHA whimpers]
Oh my gosh!
Did the androids do that?!
[GOHAN growls]
[KRILLIN growls]
[YAMCHA] It's them all right.
It looks like they just
blew up half the city!
[GOHAN]
Yeah, no kidding!
[YAMCHA]
I just don't know
how we're going to
stop them, you guys.
I hope Goku knows what to do...
Mommy! Mommy!
[MOTHER &amp; GIRL scream]
You monster!
I cleared the area of innocents
in accordance with your wishes.
Do you disagree with my methods?
[GOKU growls]
Leave these people out of this!
There are no people
left to leave out.
[GOKU growls]
Very well.
You may lead us to another
place of your choosing, Goku.
Huh?!
Wha...?! H-How did you
know his name was Goku?!
[ANDROID 20]
I know all of you.
The Namek, Piccolo.
And even you,
the one named Tien.
[sirens grow louder]
[GOKU] Hm?
Let's get
acquainted later!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Follow me!
[GOHAN] Look!
It's my dad!
[YAMCHA]
And the Androids!
[KRILLIN] Huh?!
Goku's leading them
away from the city!
Oh no!
We've got to warn him
somehow, you guys!
He doesn't know the Androids
can absorb his energy!
[GOHAN] Uh?!
[AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR]
And two, and three, and four...
One... two...
three... four...
[AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR hums]
--[ROSHI laughs]
--[AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR] C'mon!
--Go, girl, go!
--Having fun?
Burn that fat! Move those legs!
[OOLONG &amp; ROSHI grunt]
This bulletin just in!
[BOTH] Huh?
The city of Sasebo
on Amenbo Island,
9 miles southwest
of South City
has been rocked by a
devastating explosion,
the causes of which
are still unknown.
The News 8 Copter
is on it's way...
Was that 9 miles
southwest of South City?
[CHAOTZU]
Huh? Master Roshi!
That's the place
where Tien went!
I know.
I didn't want to believe it,
but it looks like that boy
from the future was right!
[NEWS ANCHOR] Communication
to the city has been cut-off
and so far, there are
no reports on causalities.
Oh no, Tien...
Ahh, I wouldn't
worry about it, son.
I'm sure Tien is fine.
Those boys know how to
take care of themselves,
wouldn't you say, Oolong?
Sure they do, and on
top of that, Goku's there!
And he's pretty much
the strongest guy
in the whole world!
[CHIAOTZU sniffs]
Yeah, I guess
you're right!
[thinking]
Well, Goku...
Once again we're
all counting on you!
[PTERODACTYL screeches]
Yamcha, I don't get it.
You said the Androids
could absorb powers?
[YAMCHA growls]
I don't know how he did it,
but when the android grabbed me
I could feel all the energy
being drained from my body!
Well what in the world
are you waiting for?
Get moving before those nasty
androids grab someone else!
[GOHAN] Oh no...
There's no time to lose! C'mon!
We've got to warn my dad!
[GOHAN growls]
I'm not so sure I want to
go back down there, Gohan.
I mean, I almost bit
the big one last time.
Maybe I should stay here!
[GOHAN growls]
[KRILLIN]
Wait, Gohan!
You stay then.
But I've gotta help...
And I'm taking
the Senzu beans.
Those two don't have
the foggiest idea
what they're up against!
And I know what those
androids can do!
[YAMCHA growls]
[YAMCHA] No!
I won't let what happened to
me happen to anyone else!
I've got to
help my friends!
Wait up, guys,
I'm coming!
Ha! Yamcha's
dumber than he looks!
Huh?
You mean you're not
going to go with them?
Not on your life, babe!
And why not?
From what I hear, Yajirobe,
you're a pretty good fighter
and they need all
the help they can get!
So I suggest you
quit being a coward
and get yourself into gear!
Can't do it.
I am tired of hearing
your lame excuses!
Get down there and
help out your buddies now!
I don't know how
to fly, Bulma!
Huh?!
I am beginning
to grow impatient.
Where are you leading us?
Very well.
This is far enough!
[GOKU growls]
I have decided for you.
We will fight here.
[thinking]
Hmm, why did he pick this spot?
Let's see...
High ground surrounded
by rocky outcrops.
That could mean they're thinking
of using those rocks as cover!
We mustn't underestimate
them, you guys.
[GOKU pants]
Before we get this
little show started,
I want to know how
you knew our names.
[thinkin] What's up with Goku?
Why is he out of breath?!
He couldn't have used up that
much energy just flying here?
[GOKU pants]
Yes, of course,
as you wish.
Though I doubt it will
matter much to you
after a few moments...
when you have been
ground to a pulp.
But if this is the last thing
you wish to hear before you die,
I will tell you.
You have been under close
observation for some time,
by a highly sophisticated
remote tracking device.
[beeping]
[ANDROID 20] This device
was calibrated to hone in
on your very distinct energy
pattern, and was planted on you
during the World
Martial Arts Tournament,
when you were still a boy.
[ANDROID 20]
From that day forward,
your every movement
was monitored,
your fighting
techniques studied,
the secrets of your
Kamehameha Wave revealed!
Over the years, Dr. Gero
followed your many battles!
He witnessed your skills
develop at a remarkable rate.
He watched as your power soared
to astounding new heights.
And by watching, he learned.
You were studied until Dr. Gero
had gathered enough information
to create the perfect
fighting machines.
Powerful machines.
Machines fully capable
of destroying you,
the way you destroyed
the Red Ribbon Army.
This is just a grudge?
[ANDROID 20] From the day you
defeated the Red Ribbon Army,
Dr. Gero dreamed
only of revenge.
We will realize his dream.
So you're supposed to be one of
these perfect fighting machines,
I take it?
Yes, I am.
I have been designed by my
creator to be superior to you
in every possible way.
A shame he could not
live to see this day.
I'm curious.
Was he spying on me while I
was fighting on Planet Nameck?
There was no more need.
By that time,
Dr. Gero had compiled
all of the necessary information
concerning your skills.
It was assumed that your power
would continue to
increase over time,
so that increase was calculated
and factored into our design.
[GOHAN growls]
Where are they?!
By the time anyone has a reason
to crank up their power level
to where we can find it,
it'll probably be too late!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN growl]
[KRILLIN] Goku,
Where are you?!
You might think you know
everything there is to know
about me, but really...
...you're not even close.
Hmm?!
Your calculations--
Did they predict that Goku
would be a Super Saiyan?
Super Saiyan?
[GOKU grunts and yells]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[ANDROID 20] Hm...
[gasping]
That's dad!
[thinking]
His power level is amazing!
It's spectacular!
Huh?
Piccolo and Tien,
you stay out of this.
It looks like they only want me
and that's exactly
who they'll get!
This is a most unexpected
development, indeed.
This technique is not
listed in my files, 20.
Nor in mine, but
my sensors indicate
that there is no
cause for concern.
Yes... It is a most
impressive ability,
but it is nothing
we cannot handle!
19 will demonstrate
this by himself!
Hm.
Heh! All right,
have it your way,
but I wouldn't bank
on it if I were you!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR]
At long last,
the battle for the future
has finally begun!
But can even Goku's
Super Saiyan strength
stand up to the awesome
power of the Androids?
You won't want to
miss a single second
of the heart-stopping action,
in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!