[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Tien kept the
monster Cell at bay
with a barrage of high-powered
energy attacks.
[NARRATOR] No matter
how hard Cell tried,
he could not escape the power
of Tien's ferocious blasts.
[NARRATOR] But Tien's technique
required an incredible
amount of energy,
and soon the courageous
hero could fight no more...
[NARRATOR] Furious at losing
sight of the androids,
Cell demanded that Tien
pay for the interruption...
...with his life.
[NARRATOR] But Goku was not
about to lose another friend
on the battlefield.
Employing his Instant
Transmission Technique,
he arrived in
the nick of time,
rescuing his friend and
challenging the android villian.
[GOKU] I'd really like to
teach you a lesson...
But I need one more day
before I'm strong enough
to go up against you!
I'm gonna take you down, Cell!
Your days of terrorizing the
Earth will be over for good.
[NARRATOR] And after placing the
near dead Piccolo on his back,
Goku was gone with a flash,
leaving Cell with
a mouthful of dust.
[CELL] Well, they won't
get away from me again.
Now I must continue my search.
[NARRATOR] The hunt is on
for the two remaining androids
and Cell won't rest
until 18 is absorbed.
Can Goku complete his
training and stop Cell
from carrying out his evil plan?
Find out today!
Thanks for waiting, guys.
Did we miss anything?
It's good to have you back.
[GOKU] Things have gotten
worse since you've been gone.
[GOHAN] Hey, Trunks,
you've changed!
I'll say... Hey, you look
like you're in great shape.
[TRUNKS chuckles]
You were in the chamber
for a whole day.
I've never known anyone who
could last that long in there.
We probably could have
come out a lot sooner,
but father wasn't willing
to leave until he was sure
he'd done all he could do.
He insisted on training
for the full year
even though it
really only took him
a couple of months to trans--
Quiet!
You've said quite enough.
Our training is not to
be discussed... Ever!
[TRUNKS] Well, I guess
you're just going to have to
wait and see for yourself.
So it worked out, I guess...
Heh, heh. Maybe.
I will take care
of everything now.
There's no need to attempt
the training, Kakarot,
because I'm sure you
would not survive it.
Besides, I can guarantee that
I won't be needing any of you
to help me take care
of the androids.
You fool!
Listen, I don't know how
powerful you think you are,
but you're underestimating
our enemies.
[VEGETA chuckles]
While you were in that room,
Cell swallowed up Android 17
and transformed.
So don't try to tell us
you can handle it.
You don't even know
what you're up against!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Clearly,
trying to defeat Cell
has taken its toll
on all of you.
That's why I am offering
to take care of him myself.
[TIEN growls]
Vegeta.
I really suggest that you
listen to Piccolo and Tien.
I mean, you'd have
to triple your strength
to stand a chance--
[VEGETA chuckles]
--[BULMA] Whooa!
--[BABY TRUNKS laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
Okay, Trunks, let's get going.
There'll be plenty of
time for fun on the way home.
But right now we better
hightail it to Kami's Place!
Hey! All right!
[KORIN] Whatta day.
Look how blue the sky is today.
[KORIN squeals]
[KORIN] Hey, young lady,
this is a no fly zone!
[BULMA laughs]
Okay, maybe that was a little
too close. Sorry about that.
Curse them! Those androids!
They escaped!
They couldn't be too
far away from here.
And I will find them soon.
[ANDROID 18] Must you play with
that disgusting creature? Shoo!
Now wake up! We have to
get off this island, 16!
Oh, great. I think you're
starting to malfunction.
All you've been doing is staring
at these birds all day long.
What do you see in
those things, anyway?
Don't you care that Cell's going
to suck me up like he did 17?!
Don't you care that
he's going to kill you?!
Oh, wow! So this is
Kami's place, huh?
Yoo-hoo! Hell-O!
[BULMA] Hey, where are you guys?
Look, it's Bulma!
Oh! Hi there!
[GOKU] Bulma, what
are you doin' here?
I brought some things for all
of you. You might need them.
[GOHAN laughs]
Hello there!
[BABY TRUNKS &amp; GOHAN laugh]
[BULMA laughs]
Oh my gosh! Trunks,
what happened?!
I mean, you are Trunks, right?
Uh, yeah.
Oh! Wow! You've grown!
This a wig?
No, it's real!
I was in the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber.
I spent a year in there, but
outside only a day had passed.
That's why I've grown a little.
Oh!
[TRUNKS]
Father and I trained together.
Huh?
Vegeta, you don't
look that different.
Why didn't your
hair grow at all?
For your information,
a pure Saiyan's hair
does not change from
the day that he is born.
[GOKU &amp; BULMA]
Oohh!
Is that true? How 'bout that?
I guess that's why you've
never needed a haircut.
[GOKU]
Hey, yeah!
But I wish I could do something
about these split ends. Ha, ha!
Try shampoo.
I don't have time to listen
to Kakarot's hair problems!
But I sure wouldn't mind
knowing why you're here!
Hold on, I'll show you!
You see, this fight with
Cell's gonna be tough,
so I thought you guys
might be able to use
some new combat suits.
And if you stop
being a jerk, Vegeta,
maybe you can have one, too.
[GOHAN] It's like the one I used
to wear on Namek! Remember, Dad?
A perfect fit!
Hey! These are
really light! Cool!
So all of these are
Saiyan combat suits?
More or less. I tried to copy
Vegeta's as much as possible.
[GOHAN]
You did a great job, Bulma!
[BULMA] Why, thank you, Gohan.
Hey! Aren't you
going to wear yours?
I am a Namek, not a Saiyan, and
I'm not going to dress like one.
That's right.
I refuse to wear
the same suit as Vegeta,
not after all of the
horrible things he's done!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Aw, come on guys...
They look good and
they fit great too.
There's no need for
you to wear that.
You won't even get
a chance to use it.
So why even bother
putting it on?
Is that because you plan on
finishing Cell all by yourself?
Well, I hope that you
can pull it off.
Right...
[GOKU] You want me to
take you over there
with my Instant Transmission?
Oh, please. I don't need
any help from you, Kakarot.
So long...
Oh boy! What an ego!
I'll follow him.
Wait!
You might need these!
[GOKU] Senzu Beans.
I saved these two for you and
Vegeta to use. Here, take them.
[TRUNKS]
Thanks, Goku.
Good luck! And if you
get into any trouble,
get yourself outta there, okay?
Right. Thank you for
everything, Goku.
And I hope that your
training goes well.
I want you to take care
of yourself, Trunks.
And look after Vegeta too.
[TRUNKS chuckles]
[GOHAN laughs]
[TRUNKS]
I'll see you later.
Yeah! Great! It's time for us
to start our training, Gohan!
Right!
Wait a minute, Gohan! Hold on!
[stomach growls]
Can we eat? I'm kinda hungry!
Aw... right now, Dad?
Come out!
I should have caught up
with those androids by now!
There's no way they could
have gotten so far away from me.
Not with 16 as injured as he is.
They must be hiding on one of
these islands. But which one?
[CELL] Come on, now!
[CELL] I am not in
the mood for games!
[CELL chuckles]
Of course!
Perhaps I'll be able
to flush them out.
18! Come out now!
I will find you!
Give up now, 18, or else!
If you do not show yourself,
I will destroy these islands one
after another until I find you!
Hey! What's up?
[DRIVER] Hey! Watch out!
Hey! Why don't you watch
where you're going buddy?!
What was that?
Something's not right!
It sounds like some
kind of evil monster!
[CELL]
Come out, you android!
Reveal yourself! I must
absorb you to become complete.
I know that you can hear me!
Make it easy on yourself!
Come out now and your
suffering will be minimal!
If you do not, you shall suffer
the full extent of my wrath!
This doesn't sound good.
Come out now!
Be warned!
No one is stronger than me and
I will find you eventually!
My powers have grown beyond
anything you can
possibly comprehend!
Join with me and end
this pointless game
of hide and seek now!
Your time has come, 18!
I will find you!
I command you to show yourself!
So that's Cell!
Heh, heh, heh.
Nice of him to let me
know where he is.
I can't wait!
Soon all will know I am
the strongest in the universe!
Not coming out?!
Then I will begin destroying
the islands one-by-one!
Do you understand?!
He's crazy!
Do not be afraid, 18.
Please stay calm.
I do not think Cell
would destroy these islands.
You are far too valuable.
He will not run the risk
of destroying you.
[CELL] They still refuse
to show their faces.
Perhaps they don't
believe my threats are real.
I'll show them.
They will learn.
Where to begin? Who cares!
All these islands are
full of worthless lives
that belong to me anyway.
Hey, look up there!
What is that thing?
Wow! He's floating up there!
Oh no! The devil!
He's come for me!
It's all over! This is it!
[CROWD murmuring]
[WOMAN screams]
[screaming]
[CELL] I don't think the
androids were on that island.
I guess I'll move on.
You hear me?!
You must come out now!
If you do not, you and
the island you are hiding on
will be destroyed!
What should we do, 16?
He's destroying the islands
like he said he would!
Do not worry.
Cell will only use a blast
strong enough to destroy
everything but you.
All other life may end,
but you will remain.
But what about you, 16? You have
to survive this blast, too.
[ANDROID 16 thinking]
Why is Cell so determined
to become more powerful?
He is already stronger than any
other creature on this planet.
What is he trying to achieve?
What is the point to
this destruction?
[CELL chuckles]
Oh, good! The fireworks
have already started.
[VEGETA chuckles]
[thinking]
I'm coming, Father.
I won't let you do this alone.
[GOKU]
This is wonderful!
[GOKU burps]
Alright! More food!
Aaahhh...
Man, that was great!
Uh, Goku? Are you done?
Oh yeah! Thanks a lot
for the chow!
Now, let's train, Son.
Right!
[MR. POPO] Right this way.
[BULMA]
Go on! You can do it!
That's it! You got it down now.
Whoa! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
You want to get big and strong--
[GOKU]
Hey, what's going on?
Well, hi there!
Hey! So you're really
going through with this, huh?
Well, Goku, Gohan, it's
your turn. I hope you're ready.
[MR. POPO]
Go on in.
[GOHAN] Ugh, it's hot in here.
I feel kinda funny.
[GOKU] That's just the gravity,
Gohan. You'll get used to it.
[GOHAN]
Look at this, Dad!
What?!
[GOKU] Talk about your
rooms with a view, huh?
[GOHAN] I don't believe it.
Is this for real, Dad?
[GOKU]
You bet it is!
[GOHAN] We're in the middle
of nowhere! It's amazing!
Heh, heh, heh! Wow!
Hey, come here!
You've got to see this!
[NARRATOR] Goku and Gohan
are about to face
their greatest
challenge together
inside the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber!
If they can endure
the intense training,
they will become
Ascended Saiyans.
But it's not going to be easy.
Planet Earth is depending
on them. They must succeed.
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!