[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Captain Ginyu, who had
switched bodies with Goku,
took on Krillin and Gohan.
And with Goku's
superior strength,
the fighting was extreme!
[yelling]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Vegeta,
thinking he was Super Saiyan,
battled the Ginyu warriors,
Jeice and Captain Ginyu.
And with incredible power,
Vegeta sent Captain Ginyu
plummeting to the ground
with one bone-crushing blow!
[VEGETA yelling]
[NARRATOR] Now, as Vegeta
attacks, Captain Ginyu
is attempting to meta-morph
into Vegeta's body!
Chaaannnggeee... Noowww!
[NARRATOR] If he succeeds,
will it be the end
of Vegeta and Goku?
Find out today!
Wha--? What's happening?!
[chuckling]
Chaaannnggeee... Noowww!
Oh no!
I gotta cut off Vegeta fast!
[GOKU] Vegeta! No!
[VEGETA] Huh?
[GOKU] Vegeta, look out!
[yelling]
[GINYU] Huh? What's
this? My old body?
Rrrr... it's you!
Yep... I did it!
I've got my body back!
What? What's going on here?
Is this Kakarot
or is this Ginyu?
Is Dad all right?!
From the way
he was hit by that
intense light beam, Gohan,
I'm not so sure!
[groaning]
Hey... Krillin, Krillin,
look! It is my Dad!
Yeah, I'm sure of it! My dad's
back in his own body again!
Are you sure, Gohan?
[VEGETA] So that means Captain
Ginyu is back to his old self!
[GINYU] I must
find another body!
[GINYU] ...Vegeta!
I must finish the transfer.
Come here, hotshot!
I want a piece of you!
[GOKU] Over my dead body!
[GINYU] What's that?!
[GOKU] Ka...
...Me...
--This I've gotta see!
--[GOKU] ...Ha...
[GOKU] ...Me...
[GOKU] ...Haaa!
Man... I'm just
not in control...
...of all of my
powers just yet...
Dad? What's wrong?!
Go--Goku?!
[GINYU chuckling]
[GINYU] Pathetic Saiyan!
You lose and I win!
[GOKU groaning]
Must... stay focused!
If Captain Ginyu changes
bodies with Vegeta,
we'll all be history!
And I won't let that happen!
[GINYU laughing maniacally]
Come and get it!
Cause now you're mine!
Change now!
[GINYU] What?!
[chuckling]
Strong work! Impressive!
Don't you get it, Vegeta?
Ginyu is letting you win
to switch with your body!
I gotta warn Vegeta!
C'mon, Vegeta!
Is this all you got?!
I'm just getting warmed up!
[GOKU] Vegeta... don't!
[GINYU chuckling]
[laughing maniacally]
[GINYU] I'm all yours, Vegeta!
[GOKU] This better work!
[GOKU] Take that!
[chuckling]
I... I don't believe this!
Ribbit! Ribbit!
[GINYU]
Ribbit! Ribbit! Ribbit!
I can't believe it worked!
Goku! Are you all right?!
[GOHAN] Talk to me, Dad!
I... guess that
takes care of Ginyu!
Just don't forget, Vegeta,
you owe me a big one!
Right! But explain
this to me, Kakarot,
what happened back
there to Captain Ginyu?
[laughs nervously]
You don't get it,
do you, Vegeta?
Take a good look at that frog
over there and say hello to...
...Captain Ginyu!
[VEGETA] What?!
Ribbit! Ribbit!
Well, it looks to me
like it's frog-stomping time.
[GINYU]
Ribbit! Ribbit! Ribbit!
[VEGETA]
Get along, little froggy!
Get a load of that,
would ya? Heh!
I'd say Vegeta finally has
someone his own size to pick on!
Hmph. Whatever.
Maybe I'll let him go.
It's not like I want to
get toad guts all over
my nice clean boots!
[laughing]
[groaning]
[KRILLIN] Goku?!
Daddy!
[KRILLIN] Are you sure
you're okay, Goku?!
I'm fine...
[chuckling]
You know, destroying
you three weaklings
would be like shooting
fish in a barrel!
[GOHAN] You wouldn't!
I... I can't believe
you would be so low
as to kick us when
we're down like this!
[VEGETA laughing]
No... He won't hurt Krillin...
Not if he wants get his
wish from the Dragon Balls.
You know me too well, Kakarot.
And besides, I may need
your Super Saiyan powers
to help me take out Frieza,
who's probably already
on his way here.
[VEGETA] Follow me!
[KRILLIN] Where we going?
We're going to the spaceship.
And bring Kakarot with you!
[VEGETA]
Well? What's taking you so long?
Can't you see
how badly Goku is hurt?!
Well, if you two
would step on it
and get him into the ship,
we can change that.
What a jerk!
Well...
What should we do?
[GOKU] Trust him.
[KRILLIN] Trust him?!
[GOKU] Think about it. Right now
we aren't Vegeta's enemy--
Frieza is!
Yeah, but...
We gotta hurry... C'mon!
Yeah.
C'mon, hurry up!
We've got to get him inside
before Frieza shows up!
In here.
[KRILLIN] You first!
[VEGETA] By tapping
into this system,
we should have Goku
up to speed in no time!
What is this?
[panicked whining]
A... needle?!
No... no... I hate needles!
Get me outta here!
[GOKU] Please!
I'd rather be sick
than get a needle!
Would you shut up already?!
I'm not even giving
you a needle!
Idiot!
Oh... never mind then...
[GOHAN] Aww... man.
How embarrassing.
[machine beeping, whirring]
[KRILLIN] So what's this
machine for, Vegeta?
It's called an
isolation chamber.
It'll get Kakarot's strength
back in no time.
[VEGETA] The liquid in the
capsule is synthetic Saiyan DNA
which will penetrate
his every pore
and make him good as new!
Whoa, mondo cool!
[VEGETA] That's right,
boys, "mondo cool".
But get a good look at it now.
Because once I'm
through with Frieza,
there'll be no need to
resuscitate any of you three.
[panting]
Have you reconsidered
about the password?
All you have to do
is give it to me...
Now tell me, what
could be simpler?
[FRIEZA] Well?
Never! I'll never tell you!
So you want to
play it rough, do you?
I've had it with you!
Now give me that
password, you fool!
Not a chance!
[coughing]
[GURU] Forgive me, Nail.
And please... be patient.
Soon, Dende will arrive
to deliver the password
to the Earthlings.
Then they can use the
Dragon to overcome Frieza.
For now, I can only hope
my heart will hold out
until we are together again...
[DENDE] Guru was right!
They're just ahead...
But I've got a feeling
there's not much time!
[VEGETA] This chamber is
one of the older models,
but it shouldn't take too long
before Kakarot's back to normal!
[GOHAN] Older model?
Uh, you don't have a newer one?
I kinda broke them...
But don't worry,
this one will work just fine.
Ah... He's not going
to drown in there, is he?
[GOKU] I was just
thinking the same thing!
Good...
Everything seems to be
operating properly.
As for you two, I think a
little armor might help you out.
Excuse me, but...
what d'you mean 'armor?'
Yeah... that was
my next question!
Gee, Gohan,
all this stuff in here
looks pretty high tech
to me! Crazy huh?
Yeah, no kidding!
Here. Put these on
under your regular clothes.
Hurry. There isn't much time!
I guess we should
take Goku's advice
and listen to Vegeta.
Don't you think, Gohan?
I mean, in the end, we're all
fighting against Frieza!
I guess.
This is the armor
I was talking about.
It's an older model than
mine, but it should work
almost as well.
Call me nuts, but how
do you put this thing on?!
[GOHAN] I dunno. I don't
see any instructions.
Slide them over your head!
And if that doesn't work,
I'll come over there and
force them down for you!
The armor's
expandable, remember?
I was wearing it when I battled
the two of you on Earth!
[VEGETA] It expands
to almost any size!
Oh cool! Stretchy!
Hey, Vegeta,
are the shoes and gloves
made out of the same material?
Shut up.
[KRILLIN] Feels pretty
elastic to me!
Man, talk about having
a spring in your step!
Just think about it guys...
We'll have the advantage
in these suits when
Frieza shows up!
What d'ya think, Vegeta?
Uh, what's the problem?!
Nothing, no problem!
I don't mean to be picky,
but your armor seems to give you
greater mobility than these.
And not to mention
it looks better.
[VEGETA] Oh, excuse me,
but, uh, last I checked,
this was not a fashion show.
Well, I think they're
both functional and stylish!
Look, you guys. See how
easily I can move around?
Uh... are you positive
you're okay?
Yes. Would you mind
your own business?
Well, sorry I asked.
I would like
to know one thing.
How long until Goku is healed?
I'm not sure.
I'd say for his
height and weight
it shouldn't take
any more than an hour.
Gohan...
I think it's best if I make
a quick trip to see Guru!
What?!
I might run into Frieza,
but I guess I'm gonna
have to take that chance!
Besides, Gohan, without
the correct password,
we're never going to get our
wish from the Dragon Balls!
I'll go with you!
No, you stay here
and look after Goku...
I'll be back!
[NARRATOR] It looks
like Goku will be back
to his old self in no time!
[NARRATOR] But will Krillin
make it to Guru and back
without Frieza honing in on him?
[NARRATOR]
And what about Dende?
Will he make it
in time to help out?
[NARRATOR] As for Vegeta,
is he afraid of Frieza or is
something else bothering him?
[NARRATOR] Will Frieza finish
off Nail or can Nail hold off
the evil warrior?
[NARRATOR] And what will become
of the seven Dragon Balls?
[NARRATOR]
Will the password be deciphered?
There are more clues coming up
in the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!