[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Frieza was in a cold
stalemate with Goku,
now a legendary Super Saiyan.
Meanwhile, Dende called
forth the Namekian Dragon
to wish everyone but Frieza
off of planet Namek,
and on to the Earth.
[NARRATOR] But Goku
wasn't ready to go,
and asked that he be
left on Namek as well.
[NARRATOR] With the planet
about to explode under his feet,
has Goku just sealed his fate?
[GOKU] I've been waiting
for this moment, Frieza!
The moment when you pay
for all the evil deeds
you've done to us!
A heroic move by Goku,
or the biggest mistake
of his life?
Stay tuned to find out!
[FRIEZA laughs]
In exactly two minutes you will
be nothing but a pile of ashes.
Just look how you're trembling.
It's you who should be afraid,
because your spree
of hatred will end
at the hands of a Saiyan,
like you've always feared!
[FRIEZA growls]
Your speeches are so poetic,
but I can assure you that
the only things ending
are you and this
ugly planet!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU growls]
[KING KAI wails]
[KING KAI] Goku, you're
running out of time!
King Kai, if Goku
beats Frieza soon,
he'll still have time to
escape from Namek
before it blows, right?
Even if Goku is a Super Saiyan,
he still needs air to breathe!
No one can survive in space.
[YAMCHA] But sir, isn't
there something we can do
to save Goku?
Goku has chosen
this way himself...
So... that's it?
[YAMCHA growls]
Yamcha!
[YAMCHA] Goku!
Goku...
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA growls]
[birds chirping]
[GOHAN] Y-You mean,
Krillin can't be...
According to the powers
of the Earth's Dragon,
any person who has been revived
once cannot be revived again.
No... Krillin...
But guys! What about Goku?
How come he's not here with us?
[GURU] Goku wished for
all on planet Namek
to be moved to Earth, except
for Frieza and himself.
Wha--?!
[GOHAN] So my dad is
still fighting Frieza?
Back on-on Namek?
Mm-hmm...
That's awful!
It's gonna explode
any minute from now!
Planet Namek's going to explode?
Great Guru, is that true?
[DENDE] No! No! Guru!
There's nothing I can do.
But... our home...
[PICCOLO] It's absurd!
Just what was Goku thinking?!
Even if he does defeat Frieza,
the explosion alone will
be enough to destroy him!
Goku...
You had the chance to escape
from Frieza and join us,
but you chose to die and
make sure Frieza was defeated...
What... honor!
Mr. Piccolo...?
[thinking] Goku...
Our paths have crossed
many times along the way.
[PICCOLO] It was because of you,
that I was even born!
[PICCOLO] From the
very beginning,
when I was
nothing but an egg,
even then I wanted
you destroyed!
I was born hating you!
As a young fighter,
those tournaments against
you were all that I had,
I lived for the
chance to see you die!
I will never forget our fight
at the World's Martial
Arts Tournament,
Ka... me... ha... me... ha!
[PICCOLO] With my newly learned
ability to increase my size,
I knew that this would be it!
This would be my
chance to finish you!
[PICCOLO] But still, you
found a way to beat me!
Your power, I'd never
seen anything like it!
[PICCOLO] From that day forward,
I knew there was something
different about you!
Something, not of this world!
[PICCOLO] Goku!
[PICCOLO] And then the
fight with Raditz...
[PICCOLO} I can't say I
objected to destroying you!
After all, It's what I'd been
waiting for my whole life!
[PICCOLO] But as you
lay there, lifeless,
it just wasn't what
I had imagined...
How could I hate someone
who'd made such an
honorable sacrifice?
Goku... Why did you have
to send me back to Earth?
I wanted to fight
alongside of you!
It's great to see you again!
I can tell you're alot stronger
now, and not just physically!
[PICCOLO] It's vexing,
but your powers have become
far greater than my own.
And so has your character.
You chose to beat Frieza
at the cost of your own life.
You're always like that.
That's our Goku...
Daddy...!
[VEGETA] I understand
Kakarot's blood!
[GOHAN] Vegeta!
[VEGETA laughs]
Kakarot just can't turn
down a good fight,
it's against his Saiyan nature!
Oh! Why did YOU
have to come back?
Why didn't the dragon leave
out those filthy jerks?!
Now, that wasn't very nice.
[BULMA screams]
That hurt!
[GINYU] Ribbit.
Huh?
And you're here too?
[GINYU croaks]
Go away!
[GINYU grunts]
[BULMA] I hate that nasty frog!
This is a nightmare!
[VEGETA] Oh, is it?
[BULMA squeals]
[VEGETA] You're all
so foolish to assume
Kakarot would
abandon a good fight!
Because the blood of a Saiyan
flows too strongly in his veins!
And now, as that idiot martyr
is becoming a Super Saiyan,
his hunger for battle
is even greater!
Nothing will stop Frieza
and Kakarot from fighting,
that is, until Namek explodes
and they both go
out with a bang!
[VEGETA laughs]
Don't laugh!
Meanwhile, since I
was revived from death,
I should become even stronger.
And once Kakarot
and Frieza are both
completely out of the picture,
I'll be the most powerful
fighter in the universe!
[GOHAN growls]
You little...!
I must admit this
was unexpected
but that doesn't mean
I won't enjoy it!
[VEGETA laughs]
[BOTH grunting]
Huh?!
[GOKU grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
So now that you and I are
the only Saiyans left,
why don't we have a
little fight to celebrate?
It'll be a perfect
opportunity for me
to test out my new strength.
Just stop talking to me, jerk!
I don't wanna have to listen
to your stupid voice anymore!
How in the world can you
think about fighting now,
with Goku risking his
life against Frieza?!
Hey, it was Kakarot's
choice to stay, not mine!
And from now on you're
all going to do exactly
as I tell you to do!
What?!
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
I'm going to have some more fun
before this place explodes!
I've always been told to
make every second count!
[FRIEZA yells]
Goku is still on Planet Namek.
But that means...
He must get away from there!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU shouts]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU growls]
Huh...?
[FROG] Ribbit... Ribbit...
Ribbit... Ribbit...
Wait, as I recall there are
Dragon Balls here on Earth,
aren't there?
So I'll just call
for the Dragon
and make him grant
me immortality!
Then I can rule the
universe for eternity!
[PICCOLO] You're too late!
Huh?
[PICCOLO] The Dragon Balls
were used to revive you,
so now they've become
ordinary stones.
It's not your lucky day,
after all. Hah! Too bad!
[VEGETA growls]
In the end the forces
of good will overcome you!
It's too late; your day is done!
Hmph! We'll see!
[BOTH grunting]
[blows landing]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[grunting continues]
[GOKU yells]
[KING KAI] Goku, you're
in way over your head!
I always told you to
stay away from Frieza!
Why didn't you listen?
[KING KAI grunts]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] Yaah!
[GOKU grunts]
Goku!
[GOKU yells]
Go, Goku!
His power is incredible!
Mr. Guru! Please tell us what's
happening on Planet Namek!
[BULMA] Goku's okay, isn't he?
I mean, Frieza can't
beat him, right?!
I'm sorry, but I can
no longer sense
what is happening
on Planet Namek.
No, oh no...
[PICCOLO] Don't worry.
[GOHAN] What do you mean?
[PICCOLO] Goku will be okay.
But how do you know?
[PICCOLO] I know.
[FRIEZA yells]
You're really a Super Saiyan.
I'm glad now that
I've finally met one.
I can see it was quite
an over-rated legend!
My dad...
Goku... please don't die...
Goku!
Daddy!
[blows landing,
grunting]
Only one of us
is leaving alive!
[blows landing,
grunting]
[FRIEZA] Yaah!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[NARRATOR} With only one minute
left before Namek explodes,
can the Super Saiyan Goku defeat
the mighty Frieza
once and for all?
[NARRATOR] And even if he can,
how will Goku escape the
firing Namek in one piece?
On the next Dragon Ball Z!