[GOKU] Be right back!
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
a mysterious boy
named Trunks
arrived from the
future with a warning:
An unprecedented force
of evil is on its way!
[TRUNKS] ...morning of
May 12th at 10AM...
A horribly destructive duo
will show up on an island
nine miles southwest
of South City.
What's the deal?
Are they aliens?
[TRUNKS] No.
They're both androids
created right here on Earth.
There's no rhyme or
reason to what they do.
They're machines
of destruction.
Man-eaters!
It's mind-boggling
how strong they are.
[NARRATOR] And while Trunks bid
a final heartfelt farewell
to his past...
[TRUNKS] Father...
I'm glad I got to see you.
Farewell, young Mother.
May the good spirits
keep you safe.
[NARRATOR] The fate of
the world once again rests
on the shoulders of
its greatest champion.
[VEGETA growls]
[NARRATOR] But is even
Goku's strength enough
to change the course of history?
Stay tuned!
[GOKU] Sorry, guys.
I guess all of this trouble
must have followed me
home from Namek.
Tell me, Kakarot,
Exactly how did you
escape from Namek anyway?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Frieza's ship was
wrecked wasn't it?
King Kai told us there was no
way you could have survived
when Namek exploded.
We thought you were a goner.
How did you get away?
Where there's a will,
there's a way.
[thinking]
But there were moments
where I didn't
think I'd make it...
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] C'mon, baby! Please work!
[beeping]
[GOKU] Work, you
sorry piece of junk!
[GOKU growls]
No! Wait! I take it back!
You're not a piece of junk!
[GOKU gasps]
Oh nooo!
[GOKU screams]
[KRILLIN] So Frieza's ship
wouldn't work at all?
Wow, Goku! I bet you
must've been really scared.
Yeah, but it's a
good thing for me
I was able to keep a
clear head through it all.
Enough with the
suspense already!
Get on with the blasted story!
All right! Where was I...?
Hmm... Planet Namek was
just about to blow...
[GOKU] Come on,
you piece of junk!
Go! Go! Go!
[GOKU] I had almost
given up hope.
But then, at the last minute,
I caught a glimpse of
another space ship!
[VEGETA] Another ship?!
Ahh, it must have belonged
to the Ginyu Force!
[GOKU] Whoever it belonged to,
I knew it was my only
chance, so I went for it!
[GOKU] There was no time
for me to plot a course,
so I just fired up the
engines and punched it!
[GOKU] I made it off of Namek
with just a couple
of seconds to spare!
[GOKU] The only problem was I
had no idea where I was going!
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU] The next thing I
remember is crash landing
on some strange planet
light years away from Namek.
[GOKU groans]
[ALIENS warble]
[GOKU gasps]
[ALIENS yell]
[ALIENS warble]
It's my lucky day...
I didn't know that the
circus was in town...
[ALIENS continue warbling]
[GOKU] It turns out I'd landed
on the Planet Yardrat,
and the inhabitants
were really friendly!
They were kind enough to
nurse me back to health,
and they even
repaired my spaceship!
So once I was strong enough
to make the journey,
I packed up and headed home!
That may explain where you've
been for all of this time,
but there's still a few
things I'd like to know.
For starters...
where in the world did you get
that absurd looking outfit?
[GOKU] It's the latest fashion
on Planet Yardrat
but I guess it does
look a little strange.
But at least it's not pink!
Never mind!
Who cares about your
stupid clothes anyway?!
Now it's pretty obvious
that you've been training!
I want to see what
you've learned!
[GOKU] Hmm...
Now where to begin... Oh yeah!
Alright!
I knew that Goku wouldn't
come back empty handed!
Come on! Show us
some new tricks, Goku!
Alright, let's see if
I can remember it now!
How did it go again...?
It's not an easy trick to do...
I like to call it,
"The Instant Transmission!"
[ALL] The instant
what?!
Hey! Come on.
Let's see it!
Okay. Watch this!
Alright, to begin with,
I need to imagine a person.
A person far away...
Now who should it be?
Someone with a whole lot of
life energy would be good!
Now... who's it gonna be...?
I got it!
Ready?
3... 2... 1...
[gasping]
--He's gone?!
Wow!
Hmph. So, what's so great about
that? It's just super speed!
Ta-Dah! Check it out!
Wha--? But those glasses
are Master Roshi's!
Yeah, they are!
[ROSHI] Nooooo!
[ROSHI whimpers]
My glasses!
But... that's impossible!
Kame house is miles
away from here, Goku.
What's up?!
It's a secret.
[VEGETA growls]
Krillin, can I trust
you with these?
Sure, no problem-o!
Oh man, now he's
gonna get an attitude!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] I'll say!
Great...
Now don't you think we ought to
talk about some other things...
like androids?
Androids?! Gosh! I guess I
almost forgot about them.
[ALLL gasp]
On May 12th, three
years from now,
on an island, 9 miles
southwest of South City
at 10 o'clock
in the morning,
two killer androids
will arrive--
[GOKU] Okay, okay!
Enough! Just joking!
We all remember.
So... What you're saying is we
should keep that day open, huh?
This one could get
a little bit rough.
So you'll have to decide
if you're in or you're out!
When the time comes,
you won't be able to hide
behind those sunglasses!
Yeah, that's for sure.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Now hold on, I don't
remember putting you
in charge of this operation.
Are you challenging
me, Vegeta?!
Hmm...
Whoa, now!
[PICCOLO] Don't
cross me, Vegeta!
[VEGETA] Or what?!
[BULMA sighs]
Hey, hold on. I just
had an great idea...
I know a way we can save
the Earth and not fight!
Get rid of Dr. Gero!
Huh?!
[ALL gasping]
Here's what I think
we should do:
Use the Dragon Balls to
summon the Dragon,
He'll tell us where
the doctor is.
We take out the doctor and
all of our problems are solved!
Ya get it?
That's great! In fact, Bulma,
I'm surprised I didn't think
of that before you did!
I mean who wants to wait
around for three years anyway?
By the time we found the Dragon
Balls it would be too late,
--you dope!
--[KRILLIN gasps]
[VEGETA] Leave the great ideas
to the great minds like my own.
Get over yourself!
You wouldn't know a great idea
if it hit you in the head,
you big dummy!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Goku, you're with
me aren't you?!
[BULMA whimpers]
Wow, I can't believe it,
but I guess I have to
side with Vegeta.
--[BULMA sobs]
--Besides, Dr. Gero
hasn't made the androids yet so
he hasn't done anything wrong.
Well, we'll just have to wait.
[BULMA] But that boy said those
androids were strong enough
to wipe us all out!
Why do you want to rush off
and meet them head on?!
Think about it, guys.
You don't want to fight them!
No, we don't. But it
looks like we have to.
[CHIAOTZU whimpers]
So... What about you two?
Are you with us?
Hmm.
We're... done for...
Well, that's it. I know
what I have to do. I'm in!
Even though the
odds are against us
and this will seriously
cut into my social life!
Y'know what I'm sayin', Goku?
[GOKU laughs]
Think about it. We're
a lot stronger together
than we are apart.
And together, we'll
have no problem
beating those
androids, right?
Yeah, Bulma, your idea
was good in theory,
but maybe you ought to rethink
your position on this one.
What are you saying?!
[KRILLIN clears throat]
[KRILLIN] Come here.
What I'm trying to say is
I wanna try and stay on the good
side of Vegeta and Piccolo.
[BULMA gasps]
[KRILLIN] I don't know
if you've noticed,
but they seem to have a hard
time controlling their tempers.
I get it. You're saying you
don't want to get beaten up!
Gohan, cool it! You're
crampin' my style!
What a dweeb. As for
the rest of you,
don't come crying to me
when those androids
take over the Earth
and enslave everybody
because I'll just
say I told you so!
Then it's settled.
We'll all fight together!
[ALL] Yeah!
[VEGETA growls]
Look at you, the great general
rallying his troops. Hardly!
You look more like
a cheerleader!
[GOKU gasps]
It's hopeless! Boys
will always be boys!
[BULMA growls]
Great! We'll meet here...
Um...?
In three years at
9 a.m. on May 12th.
And if you don't think
you can handle it,
then don't bother
showing up! Got it?
[VEGETA] Kakarot!
I want you to know just
because we've agreed
to fight together this time, I
don't want you to start thinking
anything has
changed between us!
Listen, when this is over,
we'll meet to settle the score!
Sure.
Goodbye, you guys...
See you in three years!
See ya later!
Be sure to drop us
a line sometime!
Train really hard! We're
counting on you guys, okay?
Piccolo? I need a
training partner.
So... What d'ya say?
It would make Gohan happy!
All right, then. I'm in.
Yeah! Alright!
[GOKU] Krillin! Yamcha!
Care to join us?
--[YAMCHA] Uhh...
--[KRILLIN] No thanks.
I think I'm going to
train with Master Roshi.
Yeah, I like to train at my
own pace, Goku. And besides,
I don't think I could keep
up with you guys anyway!
Okay. See ya!
Oh, and Bulma?
Hey, I hope you
have a healthy baby!
Huh?!
[GOKU] See ya in three!
[BULMA &amp; KRILLIN coughing]
Uhhh...
Bulma... what did he mean?
Are you going to be a mom?
No way...
I don't know what Goku
was talking about.
[YAMCHA] Uh, he
was trying to say...
Maybe it's about time
you got married
and started a family, huh?
[YAMCHA chuckles nervously]
[YAMCHA laughs]
I mean it's not like you're
gettting any younger, huh?!
[YAMCHA laughs]
Huh...?
[YAMCHA continues to laugh]
Hey! What's shakin'?
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[ROSHI yells]
Where'd you
come from?!
Krillin, it's not very nice of
you to sneak up on me like that!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Hey, are those
my sunglasses?
What? Hey, what d'ya know?
[ROSHI] Gimme!
Now I can catch
up on my readin'!
[ROSHI chuckles]
No wait! Train me!
Come on, please!
[ROSHI continues to chuckle]
[DR. BRIEF screams,
SCRATCH yowls]
300 times gravity?!
That's impossible!
[VEGETA] So? That's
what I want!
Kakarot trained in 100
times gravity right?
So I want three times as much.
But... That's crazy!
With 300 times gravity,
your body will feel like
it weighs 18 tons!
[SCRATCH whimpers]
Good kitty.
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
That's what I want!
[DR. BRIEF gasps]
[CHICHI] This time you've
gone too far, Goku!
I don't want you teaching our
son all of your bad habits!
I won't stand for it! I won't!
This has got to stop!
Are you crazy?! No way!
I'm not going to
let you interfere
in Gohan's studies anymore!
[GOKU whimpers]
Why do you think I bought Gohan
textbooks and study tapes?!
I even got him a "learn
while you sleep" kit
so he doesn't fall behind!
Do you want our only
son to grow up to be
a muscle bound thug
Without a brain?!
Hmph! You can go,
but Gohan stays here!
ChiChi... We need
Gohan for this battle.
It's important!
It's only this one time...
Then he can spend
the rest of his life
with his nose in the books!
Hm?
[CHICHI growls]
I don't want our son growing
up without an education
the way his father did!
Is that so wrong?!
Honestly, all the pain and
torment I go through
just because I want the
best for my little boy...
Boy I never knew you felt so
strongly about it ChiChi.
But look, Gohan wants to go!
[GOHAN growls]
--[CHICHI growls]
--[BOTH gasp]
Absolutely not! No
way! And that's final!
But... are you trying to
tell me that Gohan's studies
are more important
than saving the Earth?
That's right, mister!
There's nothing more important
than Gohan's studies right now!
If Gohan takes three
years off, he'll fall behind!
Aw relax, ChiChi.
[CHICHI screams]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] Oh no, what have I done?!
I've been in space so long,
I don't know my own strength!
There...
I guess I'm not used to the
gravity on Earth yet, ChiChi!
Listen, Goku. I'll let
Gohan train with you
but I want him to
try and study too.
I don't think that's
unreasonable.
I mean a boy his age can't
spend everyday rough housing.
He needs an education and I
want to make sure he gets one.
Have I made myself clear?!
That's one battle
Goku will never win.
Okay...
[TIEN grunts]
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN shouts]
[grunting]
[CHIAOTZU screams]
[TIEN yells]
That... wasn't... bad, Tien...
[ROSHI giggles]
Hmm...?
[KRILLIN growls]
[KRILLIN] Kame... hame...
Well, hello there!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[ROSHI] Hey, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
Why don't you give it
a rest for a while?
You know what they say.
"All work and no play makes--"
me-HAAA!
[ROSHI] Cut that out, Krillin!
You're gettin' my
magazines all wet!
[GOHAN grunts]
Ready, Gohan?
[GOHAN pants]
Yeah...
[GOKU yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOHAN growls]
[GOKU &amp; PICCOLO yelling]
[BOTH shout]
[shouting,
blows landing]
[shouting]
[GOHAN grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOHAN shouts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN screams]
[PICCOLO] Well, I think
that's enough for today.
Yeah, I'll say!
[GOHAN] No! Let's keep
going! I can take it!
I've... got to get strong.
[GOHAN grunts]
I... want to be as
strong as you two...
[GOHAN growls]
[AEROBICS GIRL] One... And
two... And three... And four!
Come on! One, two, three,
--four! One, and two--
--[YAMCHA chuckles]
Buddy, I can get you in
that class if you want!
No... Thanks.
Okay... Maybe the dance
class isn't such a bad idea.
[VEGETA grunts]
I'll show Kakarot...
that he's not the
only Super Saiyan...
in the universe!
[VEGETA grunts]
[NARRATOR] No pain, no gain.
That's a lesson Gohan is
learning the hard way
from Goku and Piccolo.
And he has three years
to get it right.
[GOHAN] Come on!
[GOHAN growls]