Huh? Kaio-Ken?
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
After the defeat of Piccolo,
Chiaotzu, Tien and Yamcha,
it seemed no one could
stop the Saiyan onslaught
from destroying
the Earth.
But that was before
Goku returned
from his training
with King Kai
and began to demonstrate
his new found skills!
I'm gonna
rip you apart!
Aahh!
[NARRATOR] Now it appears
as if the brutal Nappa
has finally
met his match.
[NARRATOR] But overpowering the
awesome strength of Vegeta
will not be
an easy task.
And with Nappa
far from finished,
will Goku's strength
hold out to the very end?
[NAPPA] Huh?
[NAPPA growling]
Aahh!
[NARRATOR] Will Goku have
enough tricks up his sleeve
to avenge his
fallen friends
and help repel these Saiyan
attackers once and for all?
Find out... today!
That's for my friends,
all four of them!
[NAPPA] I was
Commander in Chief
of the whole
Saiyan Army!
You're nothing
compared to me!
[NAPPA growling]
Raah!
[NAPPA yelling]
Hyaah!
[NAPPA growling]
[KRILLIN] This guy's
no problem for Goku.
[NAPPA growling]
[NAPPA] I'm through
with you!
Ka... ka... rot!
[NAPPA growling]
Raahh!
[GOKU] All right!
Here goes!
Haahh!
Huh?!
No way!
Ah! How was that pathetic
fool able to stop that?!
Well, take this!
[GOKU] This one's
for Piccolo!
What was that?! I didn't
even see him get behind me!
What the...?!
And this one
is for Yamcha!
Wow! No way!
He's got him! Way to go!
Yes!
Hnn.
[NAPPA snarling]
I hate you!
You hate losing! You're
not used to fighting
someone stronger
than you!
You're not stronger than
me, you little runt!
Your strength was tested
when you were a baby!
You're a
third-class Saiyan!
I'm a Saiyan Elite,
you low-class dog!
[VEGETA] Nappa! Don't
be a fool! Calm down!
How do you expect to
win when you're so mad
you can't even see straight?!
Now, settle down!
Use your head!
[NAPPA growling]
Heh, heh. All right,
Kakarot, round two!
[thinking] His skills are way
beyond what they should be.
I don't
understand it!
[NAPPA] You may
have gotten lucky
with a couple
of fancy moves,
but now I'm gonna
tear you apart!
I'm ready when you
are. It's your move.
Heh! Your time
is up, Kakarot.
[thinking] That idiot has no
idea what he's up against.
I'm sure I'll have to
clean up his mess.
[NAPPA chuckling]
Why did
they stop?
I don't know.
[OOLONG] Uh-oh, the ugly
guy's smiling about something!
I can't take it! Goku, wipe
that smile right off his face!
No! Don't!
[ROSHI and TURTLE screaming]
You fool! Why'd
you go and do that?!
Nevermind! I did it because
I felt like it, so there!
You should learn to
respect your elders!
Well, you should learn
not to shower people
when you're trying
to make a point!
That breath of
yours isn't exactly
kissing fresh,
you know!
Serves you right!
[ROSHI]
Ladies, please!
[BOTH] Huh?
I think we're all
a little high-strung!
Let's try
to calm down!
Yeah, besides, we're
missing all the action.
Goku could be in trouble
for all we know!
He's not going to
be in any trouble.
You'll see,
Goku's fine.
Now, let's see if we can
get this thing to work...
Where's the picture?!
Come on!
Hey, it's not a
television set!
All right!
That's enough!
[ROSHI] This has gone
on too far, girls!
Remember that your
guests in this...
[ROSHI] Hey!
What did I do?
[commotion and yelling]
[BULMA] I think we
might've broken it...
[BABA] No, there's a disturbance
in the Earth's energy!
[NAPPA yelling]
[whimpering]
[thinking] Now he's
getting serious.
[NAPPA chuckling]
You can't escape!
[blows hitting]
Phew! This might be a little
tougher than I thought!
[NAPPA] Ha, ha, ha! That was
just a taste of my skills!
I haven't even begun to
show you my full power!
See how you
like this...
Raaugh!
Uh?!
[bellowing]
That was fast! How could
he possibly stop that!
Nappa was right
in his face!
[NAPPA laughing]
Hnn?! Aah!
That was a little too close.
Any closer and I'd be history!
This can't
be happening,
nobody has ever
survived that attack!
He's got to have
some weakness.
This cannot
go on forever!
I should really try using
the Kaio-Ken Attack,
but I've gotta save my
strength for the other guy.
[VEGETA] All right!
That's it! Enough!
You heard me, Nappa! Come
down here! You're finished!
[NAPPA growling]
Don't look at
me like that!
So far you haven't managed
to land a single punch!
I think you've
embarrassed us long enough!
That's just great.
He was just a warm up...
This other guy really seems
to know what he's doing.
Please!
Hang on, Dad!
[whimpering]
I said it's my turn.
Now get down here!
Well, fun's over!
Vegeta's going to enjoy
killing you slowly, Kakarot!
[NAPPA] He's the only one
in the universe
that could stop me from
ending this with you right now.
He's stronger and
faster than me!
I can't wait to
watch you fail!
It's too bad he won't let
me help finish you off.
[NAPPA] Now, what
can I do for fun?
Hmm?
[NAPPA] I know!
[NAPPA chuckling]
[whimpering]
Gohan, no!
Krillin, run!
[GOKU] I'm not
going to make it!
Raahh!
[screaming]
Kaio-Ken Attack!
Now what?!
[NAPPA screaming]
How in the world
did he do that?
Good question.
I really don't know!
I-I can't
move my legs!
[KRILLIN] Wow, Goku, I think
you really hurt that guy.
He's not
getting up.
He won't be
fighting anymore!
I suggest you take him back
to wherever you came from
and get him
some help!
[thinking]
He's so confident!
How did he achieve that drastic
increase in power and speed?
[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku.
How did you do that?
That was one of the most
amazing attacks I've ever seen!
What was it?
Oh, it's the
Kaio-Ken Attack!
It's like a massive
upsurge of energy!
Everything is
heightened!
Power, speed, even hearing and
vision improve dramatically!
[GOKU] You sort of become
a super-self!
But it can only be
sustained for a short time
so you have to get
the job done quickly!
That's so great!
Do you think you'll
be able to teach me
how to do a move like that
someday Goku, huh? Maybe?
Maybe...
As usual, I have to do
everything myself...
Why didn't you
use that Kaio-Ken
to attack him in the
first place, Goku?
With a move
like that,
you could have taken him
out any time you wanted to!
[GOKU] That's true,
I could have...
But the problem is,
there's always a chance
that the increase in energy
could have destroyed my body!
But I'm still here,
aren't I? Yeah!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah...
[KING KAI] You have mastered
the Kaio-Ken Attack.
Well done, Goku...
But you must remember...
Energy and matter are
always interchangeable...
One eventually
replaces the other.
The awesome speed and
strength you gain
in the Kaio-Ken attack
come at a price...
The attack can only
be used for short bursts...
If you use it for too long or
if you are in a weakened state,
the energy will take
over your material body
to the point of its
complete obliteration.
Do you understand what
I am telling you Goku?
I understand.
It... could kill you?
[GOKU] Yes.
[NAPPA] Vegeta, give me a
hand... I can't get up!
Thank you!
Hmph. Sure. It's the
least I can do, Nappa.
Waaugh!
[ALL] Wha--?!
[NAPPA screaming]
Maybe you won't be such
a disappointment...
when you're dead!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA laughing]
Wow, this
is intense!
Dad? What's
happening?
Whoa, that guy's
powering up! Hang on!
[VEGETA] Goodbye!
[NAPPA screaming]
No! No, Vegeta!
[VEGETA chortling]
[NAPPA screaming]
Hmm. Hn?
Hnn?
Hah?! Hnn!
I can't...
believe it...
He completely obliterated
his own teammate!
[GOHAN whimpering]
[VEGETA chuckling]
[GOKU] Gohan, Krillin...
It's time for you guys to
head back to Master Roshi's!
[GOHAN] But, Dad...
I see...
Gohan...
Gohan, listen to your Dad...
Let's get going!
No! I can't go!
Don't you get it? I don't
wanna leave either!
But these guys are in a
different league altogether!
That Saiyan could even
use us against your Dad
if he got ahold of you or me
and threatened to hurt us!
Daddy?
Is that true?
Yes, Gohan,
Krillin's right.
I'll be much better off
if I face him alone.
All right...
Whatever you say.
Oh, yeah! Goku!
Don't rely on grabbing his
tail! We already tried that!
Yeah, see, Piccolo tried
grabbing that big guy's tail,
and he got hammered
for it, really bad.
[KRILLIN] They all
fought so hard.
I can't believe they're
gone! They did their best.
We all did.
But in the end...
I guess we just didn't
have what it took.
[GOKU] Then I guess...
It's up to me
to finish this.
[GOHAN] Hey, Dad?
Please, come home.
You have to win.
Don't worry.
Well, of course
you'll come home, Goku...
After what
I've seen,
there isn't anything
that could stop you.
Thanks, Krillin...
Well, it's time!
Try not to worry about
me! I'll be just fine!
[GOHAN whimpering]
You can waste all
the time you want
with your pathetic
'goodbyes'...
But you're simply
postponing the inevitable.
Its too bad.
It seems he's
totally determined
to end things
this way.
He sure would make a
good sparring partner!
Hey, Goku... You're my
friend. We grew up together!
Just make sure that we
both grow old together, too!
Right! I couldn't
have asked
for a better best friend
than you, Krillin!
Goodbye, Daddy!
Goodbye, Gohan!
I'm very proud of you!
Hey, I'll bet your Mom
is over at Master Roshi's!
Go give her a big
hug for me, 'kay?
[GOKU] Can you do that
for me, Gohan?
Yes!
[KRILLIN]
Go get him, Goku!
[VEGETA] So, Kakarot! You ready
to get this over with?
I know a better
place than this!
Wherever!
Just lead the way!
Bye, Daddy...
[NARRATOR] And so
it is down to two,
as Goku and Vegeta
prepare to engage
in the ultimate showdown
between good and evil.
Can our hero stand up
to the evil Saiyan
and thwart his plans to
take over the Earth?
Don't miss the
explosive action,
on the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!