[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan endured his most
severe training session yet!
And though the young fighter
showed vast improvement,
Piccolo wasn't
about to let up!
So you figured out how to
dodge my punches and kicks...
Now try this!
[GOHAN yells]
[NARRATOR] But Piccolo's seeming
cruelty was not without purpose.
For the veteran warrior
understood all too well...
The enemy they were
both preparing to face
would employ tactics
far more ruthless.
It's a lesson the rest
of the Z-Fighters
had also
taken to heart!
To survive the battle
against the Saiyans,
they knew they would have to
hone their fighting skills
to their highest
levels ever.
And under the watchful eye
of Kami, they did just that!
Meanwhile, far away
in Other World,
Goku continued
to sail through
King Kai's tests of strength
with flying colors!
And after months of
difficult training,
it seems the student has
finally surpassed the teacher!
Goku's strength
and speed
may have him running
circles around King Kai,
but the
question is:
Will his newfound powers be
enough to stop the Saiyans?
The time to find out
is drawing near.
The two evil Saiyans are on
their final approach to Earth!
The invasion begins...
Today!
[KING KAI]
Goku, this will be
the last day of your
training with me.
You've done well,
but I'm afraid you're
lacking in one area...
You still can't seem
to deliver a good joke
when the
pressure's on!
Everything else is good...
Let's review!
[GOKU] Hm!
[KING KAI]
'Kay... Bubbles, you're up!
[BUBBLES chatters]
[KING KAI]
On your mark... Get set...
Aaaand... Go!
[BUBBLES yells]
Whoa! Less than a
second! A new record!
[GOKU chuckles]
Next...
Gregory!
[GREGORY]
Alright! Ha, ha!
[GREGORY laughs]
[KING KAI]
On your mark! Get set!
Aaand... Go!
[GREGORY]
Ahhhh... Ah!
See ya! Ha, ho!
One-point-two!
A-Astounding!
Hey, thanks!
Well, okay! Now it's time
to test the Spirit Bomb!
I've been
waiting for this!
[GOKU grunts]
[BUBBLES chatters lightly]
[KING KAI] Excellent.
Now form it into a ball.
[GOKU grunts]
'Kay! Whenever you're
ready, King Kai!
Let'er rip!
Hm. Alright! Here goes!
Remember, Goku! Don't use
your eyes, feel it out!
[GOKU]
Right!
[KING KAI yells]
Suuuuperspeed!
Oohhh!
Yahh!
[yelling]
[GOKU chuckles]
Ohhh! I can't
believe it!
Well done, Goku!
To be perfectly honest,
I didn't think you'd
be able to handle
the Spirit Bomb
so skillfully!
It wasn't easy.
Mm. Goku, you
mustn't forget...
The energy used to
form the Spirit Bomb
is gathered from
all forms of life.
From trees... From
animals... From plants...
Even the particles of energy
that make up the air
in the atmosphere contribute
a small share of energy
to the bomb. Therefore,
you must be very careful.
You see, you have
mastered the Spirit Bomb
here on this
small planet.
But the Spirit Bomb that
you will form on Earth,
with its innumerable
life forms,
will have immense power
compared to this small one.
And if the sun
happens to be up
when you form
the Spirit Bomb,
you will be harnessing and
trying to control a power
of indescribable
magnitude
that could easily
destroy the Earth
if even the slightest error
is made in handling it.
[GOKU] Hm.
[KING KAI] If possible,
I'd like you to refrain
from using
the Spirit Bomb...
But if you must, use
it only once. Understand?
Mm. Got it! I'll stick to
the Kaio-Ken Technique.
That should do it!
Well, I'm afraid the
time has finally come
for us to say
our goodbyes...
The Saiyans will be
arriving on Earth tomorrow.
[GOKU] Mm.
Baahh!
Oh, no!
Wh-What? What's wrong?
[KING KAI] I forgot to
include in my calculations
the time it's
going to take you
to get back to
Earth on Snake Way!
What?! But King Kai,
I thought that you were just
going to zap me back to Earth!
[KING KAI grunts]
What?! You've got to
be kidding me! Right?
It took me nearly a year
to get here, you know!
[KING KAI]
Yes! But, um...
After your training,
you'll be much faster!
You should be able to
make it back on Snake Way
within two days if
you go all out!
No! But that means I'll
get there a day late!
It'll all be over by then!
I can't do that!
That's enough, Goku!
I'm not perfect, now am I?
Even I make mistakes!
Now! Let's keep our cool so we
can take the next step! Alright?
You need to
tell your friends
to wish you
back to life!
What? Tell them?
But, they're not here!
Just put your
arm on my back!
Then speak to them
with your mind...
Your thoughts will get
through, don't worry!
Uh? Uh... Uh...
Uh... There?
[KING KAI]
Yes, yes, get on with it!
[GOKU telepathically]
Master Roshi?
Master Roshi, it's me, Goku.
Can you hear me?
Master Roshi?
[ROSHI hums]
[GOKU telepathically]
Master Roshi? Master Roshi!
Eh? Goku! It's you!
But where are you?
[GOKU telepathically] Well,
it's sort of a long story.
But I'm still dead,
if that's what you mean.
I'm talking to you with my
mind from King Kai's planet.
Can you
hear me okay?
Yes, I can.
[GOKU telepathically]
Great! Did you guys
manage to collect all
seven Dragonballs?
Sure did! We're
ready when you are!
I understand that
you've been undergoing
some sort of
new training?
[GOKU telepathically]
Yeah, that's right!
And it's been going great!
But I've learned
all I can here,
and it's time
to come home.
I need you to wish me back
to life right away, okay?
Those two Saiyans
are going to arrive
on Earth
sometime tomorrow!
What?! When?!
Tomorrow you say?
But that can't be!
I mean, has it been a year
already? Oh, this is bad...
[GOKU telepathically] I know.
And I won't be getting there
until the day
after tomorrow!
Somehow the others are going
to have to hold them off
until I get there!
[KING KAI grunts]
Goku!
Ease up!
[GOKU] Huh?
I-I'm gonna pop!
Ah! Oh, sorry!
Hey, uh,
now listen...
I'm not sure how this
all going to turn out.
But I have a feeling it's going
to be some messy business.
I hope you're ready.
[GOKU telepathically]
I am. Don't worry.
[ROSHI] Ahhh...
Well, that is a huge relief.
[GROUP] Uhh...
Ho-boy. Tell
ya' what...
I, uh, I change
my mind, Bulma.
You can go next
if you want.
That's okay.
[toilet flushes]
Hey, gang! Get the Dragon Balls!
I just talked to Goku!
[GROUP] Huh?!
King Kai! That was great!
I could hear him perfectly!
Heh, heh. Well, of course.
They're going
to wish me back.
Ah, good! Well,
while you're waiting,
I have a present
I'd like to give you.
We can't exactly have
you going into battle
looking all ragged
out now can we?
Wow! New clothes?
Uhhh-huh! Heh, heh, heh...
[GOKU chuckles]
Hey! These clothes
are light as a feather!
Yes, I thought
you'd like that...
The material is light,
but it's marvelously tough!
[GOKU]
It's incredible!
Those clothes repel
attacks, too... Small ones.
Thank you so much,
King Kai!
Ahh! Check it out! You left
the turtle emblem! Neat.
Although I was
hoping that since
I've been training
under you,
I'd get to wear your
symbol now. Y'know?
Look on the back!
Ahh! The back!
Heh, heh.
What's there? I can't see it!
Your old master's
emblem is on the front,
but mine's the big
one on the back!
[snickers]
Great!
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOHAN yells]
Go ahead! Don't just
dodge! Get inside!
Haaaaa...!
[GOHAN yells]
[grunts]
[PICCOLO thinking] Darn it!
He surprised me...
That was a
reflex shot.
I didn't mean to
hit him so hard...
[GOHAN groans]
[sighs]
Hey... You cheated.
You said no eye-lasers.
And what if I did?!
You should never believe
anything the enemy tells you!
Yeah! But, I mean...
You're not the enemy.
[ROSHI] Alright...
Here goes!
Now!
Dragon, arise!
[ROSHI yells frantically]
[BULMA] Uh, I don't think
I'll ever get used to this...
[OOLONG] Yeah,
tell me about it!
Even my nose hairs
are standing up!
[screeching]
[rumbling]
What a storm! I've never
seen anything like it!
[thinking]
That's no storm...
[OOLONG whimpers]
Ugh. Hands off, pig!
Hey! C'mon, Bulma!
I'm scared here!
[GROUP yells]
[roaring]
Why have you summoned me?
Tell me your wish now!
[BULMA whimpers]
Yes, uh... 'Scuse me,
Mister Dragon,
could you possibly
destroy the Saiyans
that are on their way to
Earth right about now?
Hey, Oolong!
That's not the wish!
What about Goku,
you little pig?
What? We could
wish Goku back!
But why not wish
him back next time
and have the Dragon
save the world now?
Your wish cannot
be granted.
Because the guardian of
the Earth created me,
I cannot grant a wish
that exceeds his power.
Then I wish for Goku to
be brought back to life!
So be it. Your wish
has been granted!
[DRAGON roars]
[thinking] So they've
finally used the Dragon Balls
to wish Goku back...
Ah!
Which means the Saiyans
are going to be here
sooner than I expected!
Uh?!
Oh, good! Your halo's
gone! You're alive, kid!
Woohoo!
[KING KAI]
It's time, Goku!
Right!
Listen! Don't expect
those two Saiyans
to give you
a fair fight!
You must be on your
guard at all times!
If things get rough, just
kick 'em in the tail and run!
That's good advice...
And hey,
I really want to thank you
guys for all your help...
I promise I won't
let you down!
[GREGORY] Aww...
Oh, and thanks for the
new clothes King Kai!
I love the new symbol!
I'll wear it with pride!
Bye, Bubbles!
[BUBBLES chatters]
Gregory!
[GREGORY]
See ya'!
So long!
[GREGORY sighs]
[GROUP] Eh?!
[GROUP yells]
[GOKU]
Byyyye!
[GOKU laughs]
Woohoo!
[laughing continues]
That Goku truly does have
some incredible powers...
Not only that, but his heart
is as pure as gold!
It's hard to believe that
he was living down on Earth.
He's stronger than you
now, isn't he, King Kai?
[KING KAI coughs]
Well, he has surpassed me
in every area except one...
I am still the funniest
man in the universe!
[GREGORY]
Yay, hey!
[BUBBLES chatters
and GREGORY giggles]
Man! I feel
lighter than air!
This is great! Heh, heh!
Woohoo!
Huh?
[thinking] I almost forgot!
Every second counts!
[horns honk]
[indistinct chattering]
[GIRL] Hey, Dad?
Can we eat, please?
[FATHER] Sure.
It's almost lunchtime.
Huh?
[FATHER] Huh?
[GIRL whimpers]
[FATHER]
What was that?!
[CROWD screams and yells]
Ahh!
What happened?
Who knows?
Help me!
[BUSINESS MAN]
Wh-What is it?
[WORKER] It's got to be
some sort'a ship...
[BUSINESS MAN] Wait, you mean,
like, from outer-space?
[WOMAN] Ah! That's it!
It's a space-pod!
Remember that movie
where the plant people
took over the city?
[MAN 1]
Someone call the cops!
[MAN 2] Yeah, right!
What are they gonna do?
They'll just say it's
a weather balloon!
[WOMAN] There could be thousands
of tiny aliens in there!
[MAN 3] There's another
pod over here!
[WORKER]
Stay calm!
[MAN 1] Forget that!
I'm outta here!
Alien!
[screams and gasps]
[MAN 2]
He's getting out!
No! It can't be!
What do they want?
[NAPPA groans]
[NAPPA] My neck
is killing me...
So, the Saiyans
are here.
That means my Dad's gonna be
back soon, too... Doesn't it?
Uh?!
[CHIAOTZU]
Wow... You feel that?
Yeah. It's them...
Without a doubt!
[NAPPA chuckles]
[gasps and yells]
Heh!
[NARRATOR]
After a year of waiting,
the countdown to doomsday
has finally expired!
The Saiyans have landed!
And unless Goku and his
friends can stop them,
they'll carve a
path of destruction
across the globe in their search
for the seven Dragon Balls!
Don't miss the
explosive confrontation...
Next time on
Dragon Ball Z!