[GOHAN screams]
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
After stealing Gohan's energy
during the World Martial
Arts Tournament,
Spopovich and Yamu rushed
off to deliver the prize
to their master.
But they were followed.
[SPOPOVICH]
We did it!
Babidi should be pleased.
[NARRATOR] Not being ones to
back down from a challenge,
Goku and the
rest of the Z-fighters
joined the Supreme Kai
in pursuit of the thieves.
Although on the
lookout for danger,
none of them were prepared
for the surprise
that awaited them at
Babidi's compound.
[KIBITO]
It's Dabura!
What is he doing here?!
[NARRATOR] But the appearance of
Dabura, King of the Demon World,
merely foreshadowed
the horror to come!
[BABIDI]
I have no more use for you!
[SPOPOVICH grunts, screams]
[BABIDI chuckles]
[SPOPOVICH grunting]
[YAMU screams]
[NARRATOR]
With an army of ruthless minions
aiding him in his quest,
Babidi's dreams of releasing
Majin Buu upon the Earth
may actually be fulfilled.
But it seems the wizard has
failed to consider the arrival
of some unexpected guests,
determined to thwart his
doomsday plot... or has he?
Find out today,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[chuckles] Wonderful,
don't you think?
Seeing those faces contort
in horror like that?
It pleases me to no end how
easily humans are frightened.
[DABURA chuckles]
And they were but two!
There are millions
left to torment...
[BABIDI]
I'm so excited!
[BABIDI laughs]
This is bad...
They kill their own men.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[KIBITO] That's the
cruel game Babidi plays.
He seeks out only the
most powerful fighters...
He uses his magic to bring them
under his complete control,
and when he has
no more use for them...
...he disposes of them as though
they were diseased animals.
If he frees Majin Buu...
he will destroy
all life on Earth
just as he has destroyed
Spopovitch and Yamu.
That is Babidi's evil wish.
Oh, there's something else.
Yes?
It would seem we
have some company...
Yamu and Spopovitch were a bit
careless in their escape,
I'm afraid.
[grunts]
Above us on that cliff face
you will find Supreme Kai,
and several of his friends...
Huh?!
[chuckles] The fools believe
they're well hidden.
Seven in all.
Each of them strong...
We cannot use the energy
of the Supreme Kai or Kibito.
But three of these others
possess enormous
energy as well.
It will go a long way
toward reviving Majin Buu.
[BABIDI]
More than that, Dabura.
In these three alone, we will
find more than enough energy
to suit our purposes.
How marvelous!
[BABIDI chuckles]
I never imagined we would
accomplish our goal so quickly.
Let's lure those three
into the ship
where we can absorb
their energy...
That would be the simplest
course of action,
don't you think?
Yes...
But the Supreme Kai will
surely try to prevent it.
Oh, I think we can manage to
get around that little problem.
Dispose of the stragglers and
get back to the ship at once.
The others will come
storming after you in a rage.
Very nice.
I need but a moment,
and you will have them.
Good, good.
But spare the
Supreme Kai for now.
For what he did to my father,
I will take my own sweet time
with his destruction...
At your request, Master.
I will leave him
for your pleasure.
Shall we get to work, then?
[DABURA]
Certainly.
But! Master Babidi,
what about me?!
Pui Pui, Dabura will not
be needing any help.
So why don't you come with me?
You can fight at Stage One.
All right!
Hey, look. Why is Dabura just
standing outside by himself?
Now... let's begin.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
He knows that we're here!
[DABURA grunts, growls]
[KIBITO gasps]
[KIBITO whimpers]
[yells]
[KIBITO screams]
--Kibito!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[gasping]
[DABURA laughs]
[grunts] You...
[VEGETA growls]
[DABURA grunting]
[DABURA grunts, chuckles]
[DABURA]
Hmm... Mm...
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[DABURA]
Hmm!
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[DABURA]
Phuu!
[SUPREME KAI]
Look out!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Oh no!
I should've warned them!
--[GOKU gasps]
--[PICCOLO] Krillin!
[DABURA]
Hmm...
[KRILLIN]
Augh... Yew... Disgusting!
You're mine! [roars]
--[DABURA] Phuu!
--[PICCOLO gasps]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[PICCOLO whimpers]
[GOKU gasps]
[KRILLIN screams]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
No, Krillin!
[KRILLIN screams]
[VEGETA gasps]
[PICCOLO gasps, grunts]
[GOKU]
Guys, hold on!
Piccolo!
What's happening to them?!
Turned... to stone...
Huh?!
It's one of Dabura's powers...
Anything he spits on
turns to stone!
No, Piccolo...
[SUPREME KAI]
We can do nothing for them now.
--[GOKU] No!
--[SUPREME KAI] Wait!
Goku! Don't touch him!
[GOKU]
Why not?!
If we touch either of them now
they might break...
and then there's no possible way
to put them back together!
But... Piccolo...
[growls]
[DABURA laughs]
Nooo!
[laughs] I leave you
one chance to run!
Take it! Unless you'd rather
end up like your friends...
[GOHAN growls]
[VEGETA growls]
[CROWD yelling]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies-Ladies and gentlemen...
Please, please, people,
could you all just calm down!
[CROWD yelling]
Until the folks down here can
figure out what's going on,
we'll just take a
short intermission.
C'mon! Move it!
Hey, ref! Get a job!
[CROWD yelling, shouting]
[GOTEN]
Hey, Trunks,
what's that announcer guy
mean by intermission?
He's saying he's got to
stop the match now,
cause Gohan got his butt
kicked by those two guys.
[GOTEN] You can't
blame this on my brother!
Hello? The tournament stopped
after he got attacked,
didn't it?
[GOTEN] Stop talking bad
about my brother!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[BOTH yell]
[CROWD gasping]
[TRUNKS, GOTEN groan]
[FRIAR 1 gasps]
Uh, Mr. Mighty Mask...
are you okay, sir?
[TRUNKS groans]
[FRIAR 1] Is there anything
I can do for you?
No, I-I'm just fine,
I just slipped...
[chuckles, grunts]
--[GOTEN grunts]
--[TRUNKS] Stand up straight!
--[GOTEN] Oh, I'm so dizzy.
--[TRUNKS grunts]
I guess the pressure's
getting to him...
[GOKU gasps]
Oh, Krillin...
What're we gonna do?
[VEGETA growls]
Hey, Supreme Kai!
You said if we break them we
can't put them back together.
Does that mean there's a way to
get my friends back to normal?
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes... there's a way.
They'll return to normal
only if we defeat Dabura.
[sighs]
Is that all? Good,
then it'll be easy.
We'll have 'em back in no time.
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Let's do it, Dad.
You and me together.
I think it's time we showed 'em
who they're dealing with!
What're we waiting for?!
Let's go!
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Wait, Goku...
You'll fall right
into their trap!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
They're counting on the
fact that you'll charge
into their spaceship
to stop them!
It's safer for all of us
if you just wait out here.
[GOKU]
I'm sorry,
but I just can't leave
my friends like that.
[GOHAN]
Watch over everyone for us!
[SUPREME KAI]
W-Wait!
[VEGETA]
Sorry...
But patience has never
been our strongest virtue.
[gasps]
[sighs]
Ah, they're all fools.
Okay, let's go.
Right.
[chuckles]
Ahh, here they come!
I'd be shocked if any
one of them had a brain.
--[BABIDI giggles]
--[DABURA laughs]
[DABURA]
Trapped so easily...
[GOKU]
Huh?
[GOHAN] This place doesn't
look much like a spaceship.
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
Hey, there's nobody here...
I thought they'd be
waiting for a fight.
Hey, that looks like a
door over there...
Think we should
try and bust it down?
Uh...? Yeah.
[lauhgs]
So, you couldn't resist
the draw of a good fight
after all, huh?
You have no idea what you've
gotten yourself into.
Huh...?
[GOKU]
Huh?!
[SUPREME KAI] Once inside this
ship, there's no way out.
[GOHAN]
What?!
[SUPREME KAI] Our only hope of
escape now is to destroy Babidi.
Uh... well... that is
what we came to do...
...isn't it?
[SUPREME KAI growls]
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
I'll solve all our problems and
blow this place into oblivion.
No, you won't!
The sudden shock could
accidentally set Majin Buu free!
[VEGETA]
Hmm.
The degree to which you've
underestimated him
is astounding...
Don't you understand?
Even at a fraction of
his full power,,
Majin Buu could annihilate
this entire planet
and all of its
inhabitants in an instant!
He can't be stopped!
[growls] Hmph.
So, they've brought the
Supreme Kai with them...
How wonderful!
[laughs]
I thought there would actually
be a fight in this place.
Master Babidi...
Has the time come?
[BABIDI]
Oh... My dear Pui Pui.
Please... I'm becoming
quite anxious.
Then... let's put that
to good use...
Go see our guests and
don't leave a drop
of their energy behind.
Yes... Not a drop!
[sighs]
Look at me...
I almost forgot...
I should inject this energy
before it loses its purity.
[BABIDI]
Come with me, Dabura.
I think we know how
this fight will turn out.
[DABURA]
Yes, Sir!
[BABIDI]
Mm...
[DABURA]
Hmm...
[BABIDI laughs]
[gasps]
[GOHAN]
Hm?
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[PUI PUI laughs]
Welcome, fellow warriors.
You've arrived at Stage One.
S'bout time someone showed up.
[GOKU]
So, what's "Stage One"?
[PUI PUI] Master Babidi is at
the bottom level of this ship.
We are currently on the top
level, also known as Stage One.
And there's no way of
getting down to him
unless you beat the warrior
that appears at each stage.
You need not concern yourselves
with getting to Stage Two...
Because, unfortunately for you,
the first warrior you must face
is none other than me.
And that means that none of you
will make it out of here alive!
[laughs]
[chuckles]
All right, guys,
so which one of us
gets to fight first?
Huh?!
[BABIDI]
Mm...
[DABURA chuckles]
[BABIDI]
Huh?! What?
Half full?
We already have half
the energy we need...
Amazing. All of that
from just one shot.
Impossible.
[BABIDI]
Hmm...
And I'm wondering, from how
many hundreds of people
did Yamu and Spopovich
gather all this?
Well... it's too late
to ask them now.
Right.
But if they gathered this
from hundreds of people
in such a short
amount of time...
...maybe I shouldn't
have destroyed them.
No. You made the right choice.
The energy we gather
from those three fighters
in Stage One will be enough to
bring the gauge up to full.
It's possible that our
opportunity to resurrect
Majin Buu will come today.
[laughs]
Then we could mark today
as the beginning of the end!
You know... I've waited
so long for this,
it's hard for me to believe
that it's actually happening.
Let's see how Pui Pui is doing.
Show me Stage One.
[BABIDI] What? They haven't
started fighting yet?!
[GOKU, GOHAN, VEGETA]
One, two, three!
One, two, three! One, two,
three! One, two, three!
[BABIDI] Huh...? What?
What in the world
are they doing?!
...three! One...
...two...
...three! One, two, three!
[chuckles]
Scissors win.
Aww... I wanted to
fight this guy...
Well. Sorry you won't
get your chance.
[SUPREME KAI]
Wait, please!
You don't really intend to
fight him by yourself, do you?!
Of course I do!
What other way is there?
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[chuckles] Master Babidi told me
to be very careful
because your high energy
makes you strong and dangerous.
But you're nothing
but a bunch of morons!
The only moron in
this place is Babidi.
He didn't investigate
this planet
very thoroughly, did he?
If he had, he'd know that the
most powerful fighter alive
is standing in front of you...
[PUI PUI] You? The most
powerful fighter alive?
[laughs]
[PUI PUI] That kind of
arrogance will get you killed!
[PUI PUI chuckles]
[SUPREME KAI]
Huh?
[GOKU]
Uh?
Don't underestimate him!
Babidi uses his magic to attract
the strongest warriors
in the universe!
Hey, calm down.
Let's just let Vegeta
take it from here.
Okay?
Are you sure?
You know, none of you
will ever leave here...
And every ounce of energy
you lose as I pound you
will be absorbed by this room.
And as the energy is absorbed
it will be channeled
directly to Majin Buu.
Well, I guess that's
unfortunate then.
Since you won't
be able to hurt me,
you won't be able to
steal my energy.
[PUI PUI]
Keep dreaming!
Before I'm done, I'll do
much more than hurt you.
When you fight Pui Pui,
death is a certainty.
[PUI PUI laughs]
[growls]
This guy is really annoying.
Welcome to the end of your life.
And I promise
it's going to hurt.
[PUI PUI growls]
Ready for the pain?
The fool has no idea
what he's up against.
[BABIDI chuckles]
[SUPREME KAI whimpers]
Vegeta...
[VEGETA chuckles]
[PUI PUI growls]
[PUI PUI yells]
[NARRATOR] The fight at
Stage One has begun!
Vegeta has the confidence
but does he have the power
to survive the battle with
Babidi's crony Pui Pui?
FInd out next time on
Dragon Ball Z!