[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
The battle
against Vegeta
had become a pure test
of will for Goku,
as he desperately
sought to match
the ever-increasing power
of his Saiyan foe.
[NARRATOR] Struggling
under the weight of Vegeta's
Gallic Gun attack,
Goku was forced to take his
Kaio-Ken Attack
up one more level,
sending the dumbfounded
Vegeta hurtling toward
the edge of the atmosphere.
Raaugh! Noo!
[NARRATOR]
Battered but not broken,
Vegeta returned
vowing to show Goku
the ultimate power
of the Saiyans...
A transformation of
unbelievable proportions.
[NARRATOR] As Vegeta's
transformation nears completion,
Goku can only
stand by and watch.
With his strength
all but gone,
will Goku have anything
left to fend off
this supreme
Saiyan Monster?
Don't miss the
action... Today!
We're almost to
Kame House, Gohan.
You can make it, c'mon.
Yeah. I can tell we're
getting closer now, Krillin.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Huh?
[GOHAN] Hey, don't
slow down now, Krillin.
We're almost there.
[KRILLIN] I don't remember
that light being there before...
Look! Gohan!
Uh--Huh?
What is that, Krillin?
Is that the moon?
No, Piccolo completely
destroyed the moon...
I have no idea
what it is.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[GOHAN]
That's where my Dad is!
[KRILLIN and GOHAN yell]
[APE VEGETA roaring]
What's... What's happening?
He's totally changed.
How am I supposed to
fight a giant ape?
[KRILLIN] Something really
big is happening right now!
[GOHAN] Yeah, I feel it, too.
But, I don't think that energy
is coming from my dad, Krillin.
No, this is definitely
coming from the other guy.
But Goku will know
what to do against
a force like this.
I wish I could help.
[GOHAN whimpering]
[GOHAN] D... Daddy...
[KRILLIN]
He'll be all right.
I... don't think so.
[KRILLIN] Your dad is
stronger than you think.
[GOHAN] Krillin... I have
to go back to him.
Stop!
[KRILLIN] There isn't anything
that you could do.
[GOHAN] I can feel it...
My Dad needs my help...
If I don't go back my
he's going to lose.
I can't leave him.
But, what is it you
think you can do to help?
[GOHAN] I don't know...
But I have to try.
I can't just sit around waiting
to find out what happens.
Try not to worry...
Goku can handle himself.
Don't you remember what
he did to that big guy?
He couldn't
even stand up
when your dad was
finished with him.
Yeah... But something's...
[GOHAN whimpering]
...not right!
I'm going to go help
him no matter what!
Gohan! Wait!
You can't
go alone!
[APE VEGETA]
Goodbye, Kakarot!
[APE VEGETA roaring]
Raaugh!
[APE VEGETA laughing]
Go ahead and run...
because you can't hide.
Heh, heh.
[APE VEGETA laughing]
This guy's
really fast!
[APE VEGETA roaring]
His new form seems
familiar to me.
[APE VEGETA laughing]
If you had known what
you were capable of,
you would have never let
them take your tail!
But now it is I who will show
you the true Saiyan might!
[APE VEGETA roars]
Aah!
[GRANDPA GOHAN] Goku,
on the night of a full moon,
a giant monster-ape
comes out
and does truly terrible
things... You must beware.
We could take this awful
power from him now,
but some day he will
know the truth...
It will always be
part of who he is...
[APE GOKU roaring]
[thinking] I think I'm finally
beginning to understand.
[thinking] The giant monster
my Grandpa warned me about...
It was me!
[APE VEGETA chuckling]
Yes, I get it now.
I'm the one who
destroyed the stadium
at the World
Tournament,
and I'm the one who...
who-who crushed my Grandpa!
[thinking] Why didn't
anyone tell me?
All these years...
Master Roshi and the others,
they must have
known the truth,
must have seen me
transform into this... thing.
[thinking]
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
I don't know if there's any
way I can make it up to you...
But I'm gonna try!
Hyaah!
[APE VEGETA growling]
[YAJIROBE] What's going on
here? Oh, man...
I... I think maybe I
should help Goku.
Yeah, if I can
come from behind...
But, probably I should wait...
I need to plan this out.
There's just one
way to stop him...
The power of
the Spirit Bomb!
I just hope there's
enough time!
[KING KAI] Goku!
His only option will be
the Spirit Bomb!
If he can manage to
pull one together
and blast it
at Vegeta,
he might just make it
out of this alive.
Aah!
[APE VEGETA roaring]
Now, Kaio-Ken
attack!
[APE VEGETA laughing]
[APE VEGETA] You think
you can outmaneuver me?
Come on! You can
do better than that!
[BABA]
This is bad!
[ROSHI] Oh no,
is it Goku?
[BABA] Yes, but the
image isn't clear...
What is it,
Roshi?
[CHICHI] What happened?
[BABA]
I saw a bright light.
Did you
see them?
[BABA] Goku's power must
have increased... Wait...
But, that means Goku
must've won, right?
[BABA] Please wait...
[ALL] Goku!
Ohh, is he okay?
He'd better be...
Well, he's
not dead yet.
I wonder what could
have happened to him.
Oh no!
Look at the Saiyan!
It's incredible. How did he
transform without the moon?!
What's wrong with Goku?
He isn't fighting!
Why is he just laying
there like that?!
Tell me what
happened to him!
Tell me what happened
to my Goku now!
Oh, Spirits hear
me as I wail,
show the Saiyan
with no tail...
[BABA]
It's coming through.
Perhaps this new angle will
show us what we need to know.
[BULMA] Hey... Who is that
sitting down there?
Is that Yajirobe?
[BULMA] Yajirobe!
What are you doing?
Why aren't you
trying to help Goku?!
Rrgh! He can't hear us!
Ohh! Hey!
Oh, Goku...
ChiChi!
[thinking] Hold on, Dad.
We're coming as fast as we can.
[thinking] Gohan
sure is determined.
He's becoming more
like his dad every day.
Guh!
[APE VEGETA laughing]
Don't you think it's time to
give up, Kakarot?
You're finished!
He's incredibly fast
for someone so big.
I don't have the time
I need to concentrate
so I can form
the Spirit Bomb.
Even if the Kaio-Ken Attack
was ten times stronger,
I still couldn't
defeat him!
So, you won't attack me, huh?
Fine, then I'll attack you!
I have to have at least
ten more seconds.
I need that
time to concentrate.
[APE VEGETA roaring]
[roaring continues]
[GOKU] Huh? The sun...
Yes, that's it!
[GOKU] Just one more
look over here...
Solar Flare!
[APE VEGETA yelling]
Now's my chance. I have to
put some distance between us!
[APE VEGETA] Aaah!
My eyes! My eyes!
[APE VEGETA moaning]
This should be far
enough... I hope.
[GOKU] Fine, here we go.
The rivers. The trees. The wind.
All the living
things in nature...
Please offer
me your energy!
I ask of you...
Please!
[APE VEGETA howling]
I can't see!
Curse you, Kakarot!
Aargh!
[thinking]
I have to take my time
or it won't be
formed right...
I have to relax...
[YAJIROBE] I guess he
doesn't need me yet.
[GOKU thinking]
I almost have enough...
The power is
coming to me...
I can feel all of it
completely surrounding me...
Just a little
bit more...
[thinking] This is it...
This is my chance...
Now, while he's
still recovering...
I only have one
shot at this...
I have to
make it count.
Where is he?
[APE VEGETA] You can run
all you want, Kakarot!
But I will find you!
Do you hear me?!
[APE VEGETA growling]
[APE VEGETA howling]
[thinking] Come on,
Spirit Bomb! I need to hurry!
[APE VEGETA] I can feel
his power. Where is he?
Rrgh!
[thinking]
Here it comes, alright,
I feel it getting
closer now...
There. It's done...
If this won't stop him,
then nothing will.
[APE VEGETA roaring]
Got it!
[roaring continues]
Nghaah!
[GOKU growling]
[GOKU] Wooaah!
[YAJIROBE yelling]
Look... Look over there!
[KRILLIN] Hey, isn't that
blast about where Goku is?
[GOHAN] Hurry, Krillin!
There's no telling what's
going on down there!
[APE VEGETA chuckling]
[APE VEGETA] Well, I guess that
does it for the great hero
of this puny
little planet.
Pity, I was just beginning
to enjoy the challenge.
[chuckling]
Huh?!
[GOKU grunting]
[grunting continues]
I never thought that he would
counter attack that way.
Boy, what a
mistake that was.
I only needed just a
few more seconds
and he would've
been gone for good.
Okay, that does it. I've given
you too many chances...
That was your last.
Wow, my body feels so weak
I can barely stand up...
I must have used
up all my power
trying to draw
in that energy.
Aww... You look
so scared...
Let me put you out of your
misery, once and for all!
[APE VEGETA roaring]
[GOKU screaming]
It feels like someone's
power is starting to fade.
Yes, my Daddy's.
[KRILLIN] We're close.
Let's hurry!
[GOKU screaming,
APE VEGETA laughing]
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU moaning]
Whoops. Sorry about that.
Apparently I've accidentally
squashed both of your legs.
[APE VEGETA laughing]
I guess that means you can't
run from me any more now.
I have to admit, you've been an
interesting challenge, Kakarot.
But in your heart,
you must have known
it would end
this way.
I just can't
believe this is it.
It was great testing
my abilities and all,
but unless I do
something fast...
He'll overpower me.
Alright then...
[APE VEGETA laughing]
[APE VEGETA roaring]
[GOKU] Hrrgh!
Aargh!
[APE VEGETA wailing]
That was my last
bit of energy...
I have no more power to defend
myself against this monster.
I hope it buys
me some time.
[APE VEGETA moaning]
Damn you! What have you
done to my face, Kakarot?!
Now you're
going to pay!
[GOKU grunting]
[APE VEGETA] I'll destroy you!
[APE VEGETA roaring]
[GOKU screaming]
[screaming continues]
[NARRATOR]
Unable to defend himself,
Goku is now caught in
the paralyzing grip
of the monster Vegeta.
Is there anything that can save
our hero from certain doom?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!