[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Gotenks took aim at Majin Buu
with his peculiar
new technique.
[GOTENKS] Now for the big
finish! I'll be legendary!
[NARRATOR] Strangely,
the fused warrior spat out
eleven ghost-like
copies of himself,
all of which created a
lethal explosion on impact!
[SUPERGHOSTS]
Ah! Aaah!
[NARRATOR]
Initially Majin Buu
evaded the kamikaze attacks,
but in a clever move
playing on his appetite,
the monster was had.
[NARRATOR] However,
Majin Buu survived.
And that's when Gotenks
made a grave mistake.
Wanting to prolong
the fight in the belief
it would be more impressive,
Gotenks fooled
Piccolo into thinking
he had run out of energy.
Deliberately,
Gotenks did not reveal
his most powerful
new technique,
hoping to increase
the suspense.
And just before Gotenks could
unveil this surprise attack,
Piccolo made a rash decision.
He has destroyed the door to
the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
trapping them inside forever.
That's it. We're all
stuck in here together.
So I guess we better
make ourselves comfortable.
[GOTENKS]
Hu--!
Aaah!
[grunting lightly]
[GOTENKS]
Piccolo, is it true?
Is there really no way
out of this place?
Yes. I'm sorry. That was
the exit and now it's gone.
It's gone, Buu.
Uh! But how do we eat candy?!
We don't. There's none here.
None?! No ice cream?!
No--no chocolate?!
Nothing. All gone.
[SUPER BUU screams]
[KRILLIN]
Did you hear that?
What was that blast about?
Seems like they just started.
There's trouble!
The door has been destroyed
and there's no way
for them to get out!
It's Piccolo, he must have been
forced to seal off the room!
That was part of the plan,
right? As the backup.
[ROSHI]
Yes. I suppose Majin Buu
was too much for Goten
and Trunks to handle.
So, in order
to save the planet,
Piccolo had no choice but to
destroy the exit to the Chamber.
Now Majin Buu is trapped
in that dimension.
And there he will stay
for the rest of eternity!
Good for him!
But what about Trunks,
Goten, and Piccolo!
Have they been killed
by Majin Buu or not?
[ROSHI]
Mmm.
I'm afraid there's
no way of knowing.
But what about
the Dragon Balls?
If they're alive then
we can't wish them back!
Relax Bulma,
if Majin Buu's still alive
I'm sure he'll
kill them eventually!
[BULMA] Are you even
listening to yourself?!
Relax because a monster
they're trapped with
will kill them?!
They're children! They never
should've been made to fight!
You grown men left the fate
of the Earth in their hands!
I hope you're ashamed!
[SUPER BUU]
No candy for me?
I want candy! I need it!
Great! This is great!
Who told you to
lock us in here, huh?!
For your information I still
have my best technique!
I thought you said
you had no strength left
and your powers had
reached their limits!
I had to do it!
I was just trying to make
the fight more fantastic!
If you would have let me
I could have taken
care of Majin Buu
and we'd be on the
outside now! You blew it!
You what?! You put
the world at risk
just to be more fantastic?!
What kind of kid
are you?! You idiot!
Well, you're the idiot
that blew up the door,
so you're the idiot
who has to get us out!
If you don't, I'll use
my technique on you!
There's no way out of here!
The only door has been
blown up! It's gone! Gone!
[SUPER BUU] Buu want
candy! Want candy now!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Uuuh!
[screams]
Let me out!
[SUPER BUU screaming]
[SUPER BUU]
Aah...
What is it? A hole?!
A tear in the dimension!
Oh no! He'll escape!
Somehow he's made
a rip in space and time!
If he enters,
he'll get back to Earth.
Majin Buu! Fight me!
Ah! The hole's closing!
I knew I could have my candy!
Let's get out of here!
Hurry!
--[GOTENKS yells, groans]
--[PICCOLO gasps]
Too late.
Huh? Hey, look!
Aah!
It's Majin Buu! He's back!
He's not inside the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber anymore!
[sighs]
Did the others make it
out of there as well?
I'm not sure!
I can't sense the boys
at all. Darn it!
I wish I knew what was
going on down there!
[OLD KAI]
Impatient, aren't we?
Goku, heads up!
[GOKU]
Hm?
[OLD KAI]
Take a look!
Hey, cool!
I can see the Lookout!
It's as clear as day!
Wow! This crystal ball
sure works great!
Uh, what is that?
That thing?!
Ah! It's him! He's back!
Gross!
[BOTH gasp]
Ah! What do we do now?
[GROUP whimpers, gasps]
[SUPER BUU exhales gutturally]
You big bully! What have you
done with Goten and Trunks?!
[chuckles]
No more talk, I've heard
too much of that.
No, let's just eat.
How about chocolate?!
[BULMA shrieks]
[VIDEL growls]
[chuckles]
[BOTH grunt]
What kind should it be
this time? Milk chocolate?
Filled with cherries?
No, how 'bout dark?
[MARON whimpers]
I'm scared, Mommy!
--[BUU] Very dark!
--[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[BUU laughs]
[GOTENKS]
What do we do now, Piccolo?
I'm way too young
to be stuck in here
for the rest of my life!
Stop that! Your whining is not
gonna get us out of here!
Well what do you
want me to do?
Sing a song or
do a little dance?
Or just wait and wait until
Buu destroys the entire Earth?!
[PICCOLO] Wait a minute.
Maybe you should
sing that song.
Yeah, let's put
that voice to work.
Uh... My voice?
The vibration in his
voice caused the rip.
If we combine our voices,
we might be able to punch
a dimensional hole of our own.
Should we try?
[chuckles]
Yeah! I'm in!
[inhales deeply]
[BOTH bellow]
[panting]
[PICCOLO, GOTENKS panting]
Now! Try again!
[BUU growls, chuckles]
Which person
should I eat first?
[ALL whimper, gasp]
Mommy, Daddy!
Make him go away!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Talk about a bad situation!
Goku, Gohan, and Vegeta couldn't
even beat this monster.
So what chance
do I have against him?
[KRILLIN thinking]
But if I don't try,
then there's no one left
to protect my friends!
--[KRILLIN] Eighteen!
--[ANDROID 18] Huh?
I'm going to charge
Majin Buu. And when I do,
I want you to try to
get everyone else inside!
[gasps]
You understand?
[ANDROID 18]
Mhmm.
[KRILLIN]
And don't worry about me.
I'll see ya later, I hope.
--[ANDROID 18] Krillin!
--[KRILLIN yells]
No!
Come on!
[ANDROID 18]
Follow me!
[KRILLIN grunts, yells]
[KRILLIN yells]
Krillin!
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[MARON whimpers]
[screams]
[ANDROID 18 screams]
No! 18!
[DENDE]
18! And the child!
Oh, Mr. Popo,
none of this is right!
[SUPER BUU]
Two more sugary bites.
[chuckles]
[SUPER BUU]
Still so hungry.
[BULMA gasps]
Yes! Everyone feed me now!
[grunts]
[screaming]
[laughs intensely]
Ah!
[SUPREME KAI]
This--this is awful, Goku!
[GOKU grunting]
That monster! And we all have
to just sit here and watch!
Dad! What's wrong?
What's happening
down on Earth? Tell me.
[GOKU]
Um, uh.
There's nothing for you
to worry about, Gohan.
Everything is under control.
Uh, you just concentrate on
developing your fighting skills.
Get back to work, okay?
Uh, sure.
What about Goten and Trunks?
I can't feel their energy.
I don't know where they are.
[SUPREME KAI]
Do you think they're...?
[GOKU] I don't know.
If they're gone,
that means there's no one
left to protect the planet!
[GOKU] But I'm not going
to give up on them yet!
No! I can still have hope!
As long as we still
have the Dragon Balls!
[PICCOLO and GOTENKS bellow]
[BOTH panting]
[panting]
Nothing! And we've
been at this for hours!
You've had time to
separate and fuse again
and still we have nothing!
I'm afraid, Gotenks,
this might be
one fight we can't win.
[GOTENKS] Huh. Then I guess
I don't have a choice.
It's too bad.
I wish there was a crowd
around to see me do this!
Huh?
What are you going to do?
Heh-heh!
Just try and guess!
[GOTENKS]
Eeh!
This is no time
for your games!
Party pooper.
Okay, stand back!
Ta-da!
Ho!
[bellows]
[grunting]
[PICCOLO] Gotenks?!
What's happening to you?
[GOTENKS grunting, yelling]
[bellows]
Yeah!
What! Your hair?! Your body?!
You've been transformed!
You like the new look?
You should!
Heh! Man, I rock!
Yeah, just leave
everything to me!
Hey? With all this crazy hair
I barely recognize myself.
Ah, at least it's
better than pointy ears.
You've become
a Super Saiyan 3!
How? How did you do it?
[GOTENKS]
Ah, it's no big deal.
I'll tell you about it later.
I can't stay
like this for long.
I'd better get to work!
[grunting]
[bellows]
Aaauh...?
All right! I made a hole!
Let's go, Piccolo.
If you don't make it
through this one
I'm not busting you
out again. Come on.
--[GOTENKS grunts]
--[PICCOLO gasps]
Hello there, Majin Buu!
Bet you didn't
expect to see us again!
[SUPER BUU]
Oh, you finally did it.
[growls]
Uh?
[SUPER BUU] You look
a little different.
That's right! Not only
am I freaky looking,
I'm stronger! I'm Faster!
And I'm ready for action!
[GOKU] Great!
They made it out!
They're still alive!
[SUPREME KAI]
Look at him!
Is that appearance from Fusion?
Partly. The boys
are fused all right!
But it looks like they've
reached Super Saiyan 3!
Did you say
"Super Saiyan 3"?
Yeah, you mean to tell me
you didn't know we
Saiyans could do that?
It's kinda hard to explain
but I'll give it a try.
See, we've all gone
beyond Super Saiyan before.
But this is a level
far above that!
So is Gotenks
stronger than you?
Well, I can do it too.
But these boys... Wow!
They've pushed
themselves to a point
I couldn't even reach until
my entire life was over!
I sure am proud of them!
[GOKU]
My little son!
Oh boy, Majin Buu's
gonna get it now!
[gasps]
[grunts]
Look at this place.
Completely ruined, again.
[PICCOLO grunting]
Where is everyone?
What have you done to them?
[chuckles]
They're in me.
[gasps horiffied]
What? You mean you ate them?!
Yes, everyone.
Tasty!
[burps]
[GOTENKS]
And my mom? Her too?
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
Everyone.
[GOTENKS grunting]
[PICCOLO]
Gotenks!
[GOTENKS grunting]
[GOTENKS grunting intensifies]
--[SUPER BUU chuckles]
--[GOTENKS continues grunting]
[GOTENKS continues grunting]
[PICCOLO gasps]
Buu! You'll pay for each one!
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu's
lethal cravings have
pushed Gotenks over the edge.
With friends and family resting
in the monster's belly,
the young fighter has only
one thought on his mind...
Revenge.
Is Majin Buu about
to meet his match
in a child Super Saiyan 3?
Find out, when
Dragon Ball Z continues!