[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu realized that he
no longer needed any guidance
from his master, Babidi
and decided, much to
Babidi's dismay,
that the evil wizard
was expendable.
[NARRATOR]
Suddenly free, with no one
to put a damper on his fun,
Majin Buu celebrated his
newfound independence
the only way he knew how:
with massive destruction!
[NARRATOR]
Back at The Lookout,
Goku learned that
because he had used the
energy-draining Super
Saiyan 3 to stall Majin Buu,
he had even less time remaining
on Earth than he thought.
[GOKU]
Thirty minutes?! Ah!
Is that all the time I've got?
[NARRATOR] Determined to make
the most of every last second,
Goku started training
Goten and Trunks
in the art of fusion.
Only by mastering this technique
can the boys hope
to defeat Majin Buu
once Goku has returned
to the Other World.
[NARRATOR] These complex moves
will take time to perfect.
Unfortunately, time
is the one thing
the Z Fighters
absolutely don't have.
[TRUNKS]
This might be a bit tough.
[GOKU]
Listen, boys!
You two are gonna
have to face off
against Majin Buu
in just two days.
Now, that's pretty soon.
[panting]
So it's crucial you know
how to fuse before then.
Do you understand?
[BOTH]
Yes!
[panting]
[PICCOLO thinking] Listen
to that. He sounds pathetic!
I still can't believe
how much energy Goku lost
becoming a Super Saiyan 3.
[GOKU] Okay guys, I hope you
were paying close attention.
You're gonna have to
do the same exact moves,
in perfect symmetry.
All right? Let's give it a try!
[BOTH]
Uh...
Hm? What's wrong?
[TRUNKS] Uh, I don't think Goten
knows what symmetry is, sir.
Huh? Oh, right.
Well, it's--
How should I put it?
[GOKU] It's like--
Well, no. Mirrors and--
Oh! I've got it, Piccolo and
I can show you how it's done!
Huh?!
A-Are you sure?
[TRUNKS thinking]
This, should be good.
[GOKU]
Now, watch us very carefully.
We only have time to
demonstrate this once.
Just follow me,
Piccolo, and do what I do.
But in reverse,
like a mirror opposite.
Fu...
...sion!
Ha!
[GOKU]
That is symmetry!
[KRILLIN]
What the heck was that?!
Is this fusion or
a junior high prom?
I don't know how
I feel about that
being our last hope
to save the world.
Now, are you two ready
to give it a try?
[BOTH]
Yeah!
Goku, would you have
really asked Vegeta
to do this fusion move with
you if he were still alive?
It's just that--
Well, I can't imagine
Vegeta subjecting himself
to something like this.
Hm? Why not?
What's wrong?
It's sort of...
[GOTEN]
Hey, Dad, look at this!
[TRUNKS]
Right?
That's it!
Oh. But, Goten, your left
arm is a little bit low!
It should be even with Trunks's.
Good! Now take three steps.
Fu... sion!
[GOTEN]
Oops!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS chattering]
Oh, brother!
[GOKU] All right! Let's take
it again, from the top.
Remember, symmetry!
[CHICHI groans]
Gohan! Gohan!
ChiChi. My poor girl.
She's going to have
to speak a lot louder
for him to hear
in the Other World.
Huh? Oh, it's you.
Can you tell me how much time
Goku has left with us, Baba?
Well, judging from
his energy level,
I'd say about 15 minutes.
Just 15?!
ChiChi! Oh, please
snap out of it soon!
Otherwise you'll wake up to
another one of your boys gone.
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fu...
...sion!
Ha!
Mm-hm! Now, that was much
better than before!
[GOKU]
Just keep doing it like that!
I wish they'd hurry!
If Goten weren't
holding my Trunks back
they'd be ready to
fight Majin Buu right now
and could keep all those
people from getting killed.
Somebody's gonna
have to hold me back
if she keeps talking like that.
[BUU laughs]
This planet more fun with no
Babidi tell Buu what to do!
Buu never so happy
in Buu's whole long life!
So much to boom! Boom-boom!
Where, oh where, oh where do
Buu take nice visit to next?
Buu!
So many places for Buu to visit!
[yawns]
Buu need a little sleepy now!
[BUU] This look like nice
place to sleepy-sleep.
[DIVER humming]
[yelps]
Hey, wide load! Start walkin'!
Uh...
[growls] Come on!
Didja hear me? This ain't no
truck stop, so keep on movin'!
You want help Buu move?
Uh... What the--? Are you crazy?
Look, I got a load to deliver
and I'm on the clock
so you don't get outta my way
you're gonna be road kill.
I'm serious you underst--?
[BUU growls]
Majin Buu!
Please don't!
[DRIVER]
I want my union rep!
It's that feller
from the vision! Ah!
[yelps]
Ooooh!
[BUU] ♪ Buu, Buu-Buu-
Buu-Buu-Buuuuu. ♪
[CROWD screams]
Yes! Buu like it here!
Now time to build home
and take quiet nap.
[CROWD screaming]
No more noise!
They build home for Buu!
[CROWD screaming]
You make Buu house!
[panting]
[screams]
[DRIVER]
We didn't do nothin' wrong!
Now Buu put you people to use!
[BUU cackles]
Mold!
Now to do landscaping.
[BUU]
Pretty!
[BUU humming]
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fu... sion! Ha!
[GOKU] No, no, that's
not it. Try it again.
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fu...
...sion!
Ha!
Hum. That's still not right.
You're breathing has
to be absolutely in sync.
Goten, ask your dad
if we can take a break.
Mm-mm! You ask!
Hey! Attention!
[BOTH]
Sir, yes, sir!
[BUU humming]
[BUU]
Buu all done!
Buu's house!
[screams]
[BUU]
Aha! The house that Buu built!
[BUU] Next time make
door closer to ground.
[BUU] Buu want food!
Buu want food! Buu want food!
Ah!
Oh, wait. Buu should
wash before eat.
Bubbles take edge off.
Just like bath water!
There you go little toes!
Buu feel so fresh and so clean
in brand new pajamas! Pop!
Makes Buu feel all
warm cuddly on inside.
So soft and comfy
against Buu's clean skin
just like wearing a thin
red layer of fluffy clouds.
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-ja-mas!
Look! It Buu!
Privacy please!
[BUU grunting]
[BUU sighs]
What relief to finally
clean Buu's teeth
after so much yum-yums!
Smell Buu's breath! Minty fresh!
Buu go sleep!
[snoring]
Buu sleep good!
Feel well rested.
If Buu sleep for night.
Then today must be tomorrow
and that's one day
after yesterday was!
Where is the strong guys at?
Right! That little man said
they here in two days!
And that yesterday so
tomorrow they here!
[GOKU] Start over again
from the top, guys.
And remember this time to stay
in time with the rhythm. Ready?
[clapping in time] One-two.
One-two. One-two.
One-two. One-two. One-two.
One-two. One-two. One-two...
What's the matter, Trunks?
I'm sorry, but this
Fusion technique's lame.
What? You think it's lame?
Ha! Kids today! Ah!
Fusion is anything but lame.
The Metamorese people
who taught this to me
are some of the strongest
warriors in the universe,
thanks to Fusion!
Okay. But, first
can you show me
h-how you change
into Super Saiyan 3?!
Those people may be powerful,
but they're no
Super Saiyan 3!
Hey, can you show me
how to do it too, Dad?
Instead of wasting our time with
this boring old Fusion thing,
wouldn't me and Goten
be a lot better off
if we became
Super Saiyan 3?
Yeah! I'm sure we
can beat Majin Buu then!
[laughing]
You can't!
[BOTH]
Huh?
The only way you two
boys can beat Majin Buu
is by fusing together!
Just trust me on this one.
Maybe, your dad is right.
Great! Take it from the top!
They look so sad, fine!
I'll show you the
Super Saiyan 3 just one time.
Wow!
Go Dad!
[GOKU]
Not so fast.
You have to promise me
that you'll really
learn to fuse afterwards.
Promise!
Be smart, Goku!
You'll lose what little
time you have left on Earth.
I'm already out
of time, Piccolo.
Trunks, Goten! Watch closely!
First, turn Super Saiyan!
[GOKU yells]
Then you go one step beyond
that to a Super Saiyan 2:
an Ascended Saiyan.
[BOTH]
Uh-huh.
Then...
[yells]
I'm... afraid!
[GOKU] This next energy
has to come deep inside.
Push hard to find it!
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[GOKU yells]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[gasps]
[GOTEN, TRUNKS grunt, gasp]
Tap into that and you
become a Super Saiyan 3.
--[TRUNKS] That's awesome!
--[GOTEN] Cool, Dad!
[GOKU grunts]
What's wrong?!
Daddy!
Goku!
[panting]
Don't worry about me,
I'm all right.
Let's get back to work.
You two promised me, remember?
[BABA]
Goku!
Your time's up, Goku!
Now?!
That little stunt
you just pulled
drained the last grains of
sand through your hourglass.
Alright, Piccolo just pick up
where I left off, okay?
I know these boys
aren't too graceful
but they learn fast
and I believe in them!
But, Goku...
I'm putting all of my trust
in you with this one, Piccolo.
You've earned it!
Thank you.
Trunks and Goten.
I know you'll show Piccolo
the same respect and dedication
that you've shown me.
He's the one in charge now.
[BOTH]
Yes!
[groaning]
ChiChi! Please wake up, darling!
Wh-Where am I, Dad?
I'll explain everything later
when we have more time.
But for now, let's--
Goku's gotta go back
to the Other World now!
What?! Goku's leaving?!
[OX KING groans]
[ROSHI] Things aren't the same
around here, without you, Goku.
These guys won't
let me have any fun.
[BULMA]
We'll miss you!
Goku, you still think about us
when you're in Other World,
uh, don't you, buddy?
Yeah!
Goku! Nooooo!
[CHICHI sobs]
But, Goku... Goku, how
can you say goodbye?
Now that Gohan has left me too?!
ChiChi, you'll be all right
you still have Goten
to look after you.
And what if Majin Buu takes
him away from me like Gohan?
That won't happen!
Once he masters Fusion, Goten
can't possibly lose the fight!
I'll tell Gohan how
much you really miss him
when I see him there.
You won't. I know. Gohan is
still alive, I'm sure of it!
Oh? But how?
[VIDEL] I don't know, I just
feel him beating in my heart.
To be young and in love!
To be completely irrational.
Boy, I miss those days, a lot.
Your devotion to
him is really great.
Thank you, sir.
Hey, no more goodbyes!
Your time's up.
But--
Huh? What is it, Goten?
Oh, I know!
You want one last hug from
your father, don't you, Goten?
Oh, of course!
Hey, there's nothin' to be
ashamed of, son. It's okay.
Goten, gonna take
care of Mom for me?
Goku, you can't put
it off any longer!
Gotcha.
[GOKU]
I'm proud of you, son.
So long, everybody!
[ALL] Goodbye! Bye, Goku!
Nice seeing you, bye!
[GOKU]
Good luck fighting Majin Buu!
I'll see you all
sooner or later!
Ha, where you're going, I hope
it's a bit later than sooner!
[ALL]
Goodbye! I miss you!
Buu gonna run out
of things to boom
if strong guys
don't come soon!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu continues
to ravage the Earth!
But elsewhere, on the
World of the Kais,
deep in the heart
of the universe
plans are being
made to stop him.
[NARRATOR]
Gohan continues his training
with the mighty Z Sword.
Will it be enough to crush
Majin Buu once and for all?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball Z!