You make Buu house!
[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
the town folk were
going nowhere fast
as they tried
in vain to escape
the evil clutches
of Majin Buu!
[BUU]
Buu put you people to use!
[NARRATOR] It was a bad day
for the helpless citizens,
who were transformed
into giant lumps of clay!
And what did the diabolical
Buu intend to do
with this great
ball of humanity?
Why construct a
dwelling, of course!
The proud new neighbor
was moving in!
Meanwhile, in the
safety of the Lookout,
Goku was teaching Trunks and
Goten the Fusion Technique!
[GOKU] That's it! Oh.
But Goten, your left arm
is a little bit low!
[NARRATOR] A mastery of the
Fusion Technique would allow
Goten and Trunks to unite
and become one super being!
But before Goku could
complete their training,
it was time for
him to depart
and return to
the Other World!
[GOKU] Hey, there's nothin'
to be ashamed of, son.
Goten, gonna take
care of Mom for me?
Goku, you can't put
it off any longer!
Gotcha.
[NARRATOR] And so,
Goku's magical day on Earth
came to an end!
It was a time of both
joy and sorrow
for his family and friends!
[GOKU] I'll see you
all sooner or later!
Huh? Wow!
Look at that line!
There must be millions of them!
[ATTENDANT 1]
Please remain calm!
[gasps] That's a whole lot
of dead folks, Baba!
[BABA] Yep, they're dying
like flies down there.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU]
What's that thing made out of?
I almost bit my tongue off!
Why'd you put the brakes
on like that? What's up?
[BABA] I'm having second
thoughts, that's all.
[GOKU]
Huh?
Well, look! I don't
want to be a worrywart!
But I don't feel
comfortable leaving
Trunks and Goten
to fight Buu alone!
Oh, so that's what's
buggin' you, is it?
Well, if the two boys
learn the Fusion Technique,
there won't be
anything to worry about!
Are you kidding?
Do you really think
that those little tykes
can defeat a powerful
monster like Majin Buu?
[GOKU]
Mm-hm!
[BABA]
I see.
Hmm! All right, then! Let's go!
[SOULS chattering]
Goku, I'm surprised at you!
You're not going to
cut in line, are you?
I sure am!
But don't tell!
[BABA laughs] You crack me up!
I'll see you later!
Hey! Thanks for
the great day, Baba!
It was definitely one
to remember! So long!
[ATTENDANT 2] Please approach
in an orderly fashion!
I know it's a long wait, but
you're dead. So, just relax!
All right, knock it off out
there, you bodiless tramp!
Single file! It's not too late
to be sent down below, you know!
[ATTENDANT 3] Why do
people lose their manners
when they lose
their bodies? Huh?
Hey! It's you!
Yeah! Nice to see
ya again! Bye!
[ATTENDANT 3] Wait! The back of
the line's the other... way!
[ATTENDANT 4]
Move along! Next!
[YEMMA groans]
[ATTENDANT 4] Please wait for
King Yemma to address you.
[GOKU]
Hey, King Yemma!
[YEMMA]
Hm?
Oh! It's you, Goku!
And what brings you here today?
Well, I have a favor to ask!
Could you see if my son,
Gohan, came through here?
What? Do you know
what you're asking of me?
Look! These are
just from today!
Look at that line!
There are millions of them!
They just keep coming!
Yeah, Earth is under siege!
It's pretty bad.
I wouldn't be surprised if the
whole population ended up here
before too long!
What?
[SOULS yelp]
[ATTENDANT 5]
Ow!
[YEMMA]]
The whole population! Oh...
Well, King Yemma!
My son Gohan can
help to avoid that,
but I don't even know
if he's still on Earth!
That's why I need your help!
Do you mind seeing if
he's checked in yet, please?
Oh, all right! Hmm. Gohan?
[YEMMA] Let's see here.
G... O... Gohan, hmm...
What a mess! I don't write
well when I'm under pressure!
I don't see a Gohan.
Unless he's on the next page.
No! He's not here!
It's true that I've been
working around the clock,
but I think I would
have remembered
if your son checked in!
Really? He's not dead?
Woo-hoo! Yeah, yeah!
He's not dead! Awesome!
Oh, and Goku!
A hard case came
through a while ago!
Name's Dabura! I think
you know this guy?
Ah, yeah!
[YEMMA]
I knew it!
He was a handful,
I can tell you that!
Listen! You better behave
yourself in here! Understand me?
[YEMMA]
He was supposed to go below.
But he would have enjoyed that
so I gave him my
stamp of approval
and admitted him up here!
Nice goin', King!
[GOKU] Thanks, King Yemma!
See ya later!
[YEMMA]
Goodbye, Goku!
[GOKU laughing]
Woo-hoo!
Haaaa!
All right! Yeah!
I can't believe it! Gohan is
still alive! This is great!
[GOKU laughing]
Yeah!
Videl was right.
He's alive. Smart girl.
Wait! If he's alive
why haven't I been able to
sense his energy anywhere?
Hmm? Let's see!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Whoa! That's Gohan, all right!
There's no mistake about that!
But it feels like he's
up here somewhere!
Not on Earth! Hm?
Wow! That's weird!
Supreme Kai must be
behind this! No doubt!
Instant Transmission!
You've gotta love it!
[grunting]
[grunting, panting]
[yelps]
[BOTH gasping]
[GOHAN]
Dad! What are you doing?
Dad?
Who, me? Oh, no, nothing!
Just, uh, trying
to keep my head!
Hey, look at those fancy
new clothes! Wow!
Supreme Kai gave
me these! Cool, huh?
Huh? Kai's here?
Oh, yeah! Sure enough!
Hello there, Supreme Kai!
[SUPREME KAI]
Greetings, Goku!
It defies all logic!
How-How did he get here?
It's not possible!
[GOKU]
How strange! What is this place?
[GOTEN]
It's a special sanctuary, Dad!
But why are you here?
Twenty-four hours aren't up yet!
What's goin' on down there?
Well, son, nothing good!
Everywhere Majin Buu goes
he leaves a path of death and
destruction in his wake!
Goten and Trunks are trying to
perfect the Fusion Technique,
but in the meantime,
millions and millions of
innocent people are dying!
He won't stop!
Not until they're all dead!
Every last one of them!
Huh?
Hey, can I check that
sword out, Gohan?
[GOKU]
Gohan? Hello?
Huh? Oh. Yeah!
Sorry, Dad! Here!
Be careful though.
It's kinda heavy!
[GOKU]
It sure is a beauty!
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU]
Woah! You weren't kidding!
Really could hurt yourself
swinging this thing around!
Unless you put your body
behind it like this!
[GOKU grunts]
[SUPREME KAI, KIBITO gasp]
[GOKU]
Yeah!
[GOKU] Now, that's a...
a little easier.
[KIBITO thinking]
First Gohan, now him!
How can he wield the
Z Sword in such a manner
without any previous training?
This is truly remarkable!
[GOKU grunting]
Nice sword!
Hey, do you mind if I
stay here with Gohan?
Just until he's ready
to fight Majin Buu?
Yes, of course! That would
be a very big help!
I do have one more request!
It has to do with optimizing
our training regimen!
Do you think you could give
us something good to eat?
[SUPREME KAI]
Uh, yes! Why not?
Shall we take a
little break, Gohan?
Sure!
Follow me, then!
We'll round something up!
[GOTEN] So, Dad! What's it like
becoming a Super Saiyan 3?
I'll bet it's pretty wild!
It is! It's great!
I'll show you how to do it
after we get a bite to eat!
[snoring]
[PICCOLO]
Well, what do we have here?
[PICCOLO growling]
[yells]
[PICCOLO] What do you two
think you're doing?
Get up, you lazy scoundrels!
Up! Up! Up! Up!
Now! I don't want
you two resting again
until you're one person!
Do I make myself clear?
Well? Do I?
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Yes...
[PICCOLO] Don't expect me to be
soft on you like Goku was!
You're in Piccolo's
training camp now,
and we don't rest
until we succeed!
And we will succeed!
Understood?
[snoring]
[PICCOLO]
Huh? I don't believe this!
They haven't heard
a single word I've said!
All right, you two! Get up!
You heard me! Wake up!
You guys can go back to
sleep now if you'd like!
No thanks! We're not tired!
[PICCOLO] Well, now! That's what
I like to call dedication!
You're sure to succeed
with that attitude!
[GOTEN]
What's for breakfast?
[PICCOLO]
Breakfast?
You're having the Fusion
Technique for breakfast!
That's what!
Wow! Looks like Piccolo's
really gettin' into
the spirit, isn't he?
Now! Let's get
started, shall we?
[TRUNKS]
Um... Piccolo?
--[PICCOLO] What?!
--[TRUNKS] Um, before we begin,
[TRUNKS] would you mind
demonstrating the proper way
to do the Fusion
Technique for us?
[PICCOLO gasps]
If this is your training camp,
you need to teach us!
We've only seen the
technique done right once!
Yeah, Trunks is right!
How are we supposed
to learn the technique
if we've only seen
it done one time?
[grunting]
[BOTH]
Please!
Krillin! Come here!
Who? Me?
You saw Goku
demonstrate the form!
Don't tell me you
forgot it already?
No! Of course, I remember!
Who could forget?
But, why me? Everyone
here has seen that pose!
Hey! Eeee! They're gone!
--Hey! Yo guys? Eeee!
--[PICCOLO] Krillin!
[groans] All right! I guess
it's for a good cause.
[BOTH laugh]
Okay! Are you boys ready?
[BOTH]
Yeah!
Let's see now!
No, it was the other way!
Let's do it, Krillin!
Oh! Right!
[PICCOLO, KRILLIN]
Fu... sion! Ha!
Oh, man! If grown men
look like sissies doin' it,
just think how we look!
They look funny!
This is ridiculous!
Are we finished yet?
Hey! How do you think I feel?
I've had to do this twice!
Deal with it!
All right! You've had your
example! Now get busy!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Right!
[TV ANCHOR]
Majin Buu has attacked again!
And here are some live images
from the scene of the monster's
most recent assault!
The horrible Majin Buu has
already killed two thirds
of the Earth's population!
If this hideous
beast isn't stopped--
Hey! Hey wait! Wait a minute!
St-- Wait! Aaaahhh!
Oh, no!
[CROWD screams]
[BUU]
Buuuuuuu!
[BUU humming]
Huh?
Oh, boy! Buu see boy!
Ha, ha! Buu play with boy!
Make dead! Yeah!
[BUU laughs]
Hi! What's your name?
My name's Tommy!
Hmm? Everyone know Buu!
Everyone? That's a whole
lot of people! I'm impressed!
Hey, I know! I bet
you're famous, aren't you?
You no fool Buu! You no
see 'cause eyes closed!
Boy open eyes!
Even if I opened 'em I still
wouldn't be able to see you.
Haven't you ever heard
of a blind kid before?
Huh? You no scared
'cause you no see! Well!
[TOMMY] Whoa! What's going on?
That feels strange!
[BUU]
Mm!
Hey! What'd you do?
Ohh! Buu make boy
see through eyes!
[TOMMY]
But that's impossible!
[BUU]
No! Buu can do!
Boy make eyes open!
[TOMMY] Huh? I-I don't
believe it! I-I can see!
This is incredible! I can see!
I can see everything! Your feet!
The ground! My hands!
[laughs]
Now! Boy look at Buu!
Yes! I can see you!
Huh?
[TOMMY]
You healed me! Thank you!
It's a miracle! Now I
know why you're famous!
You're a great, great man!
Boy not scared?
[TOMMY]
Mister Buu, are you a foreigner?
Who? Buu?
Uh-huh!
You have different hair than
mine, and different skin!
Buu!
Huh?
Is Buu hideous?
Gosh, I don't know, Buu!
You're the first
person I've ever seen!
But, hey! I know you're
beautiful on the inside!
Oh? Buu like you!
Buu like you! Ahhhh!
Oh, hey! I have
something for you!
For Buu?
[TOMMY] Yeah, to pay you
back for helping me to see!
I was gonna buy milk with it,
but I'd rather give it to you!
Oh, here it is! Ahh!
No like!
Bleh! Bad!
Boy stay! Buu come back!
[TOMMY]
Oh! He can fly!
Wow! That means he's
a superhero! Awesome!
Aha!
[PRODUCE MAN]
Ho, diddley!
It looks like I might actually
make it home on time tonight!
Let's see! Yep!
This one goes-- Hmm?
[yelps] It's you!
Turn into milk!
[laughs]
Hey! He's back! Wow!
Buu! Buu bring milk!
Boy drink milk! Yes! Yes!
Well, sure! Why not?
Yes! Boy why not!
Buu got milk! Give boy!
Thanks!
[TOMMY]
Hey, wait! Where are you going?
Don't leave me, Buu!
Please! Come back!
All I had to eat
today was an onion.
No hideous! Buu beautiful!
Woo-hoo!
[BUU giggles]
[BUU cackles]
Yay! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Buu make boom!
[GOHAN grunting]
That's much better!
Now, let's do it one more time!
All right?
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Yes, sir!
[NARRATOR] As Majin Buu
continues his wanton destruction
of the Earth, Trunks and
Goten further their quest
to perfect the
Fusion Technique!
But will the boys be able to
master the technique in time?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!