[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
it was a narrow escape for
Goku on the planet Namek
after a dreadful
attack from Frieza.
[NARRATOR] Behind the
veil of a smokescreen
Goku made an
important discovery:
He learned that Frieza was
unable to "feel" his whereabouts
by sensing his power signal.
[NARRATOR] It wasn't
much of a weakness,
but against an
opponent like Frieza,
opportunities of
advantage are rare.
[NARRATOR] Once again Frieza
fired with amazing power,
and this time it looked like
he was going to hit his target!
[GOKU grunts]
[NARRATOR] But with sheer
determination and true grit,
Goku held on to the
immense force of the attack!
[NARRATOR] As he struggled
to contain the energy
pushing against him, the entire
planet began to come apart!
[GOKU grunting]
[NARRATOR] After seeing his
attack thwarted by Goku,
Frieza continued his
relentless assault.
Hey! Goku! Look out!
[GOKU] Hey, just what's
your deal anyway, Frieza?
[NARRATOR]
The battle continues... today!
[CHICHI] Panties, shades,
camera, sushi, coffee...
Alright, I'm ready.
I'll get Gohan and
bring him back myself!
ChiChi, really. I think
it'd be wise to reconsider.
The planet Namek is certainly
no place for a lady.
He's right!
Goku can handle things
up there! Have faith in him!
I remember one time
when my poodle was lost.
I know how you feel.
But it all works out in the end.
It does? Yeah, right...
Not in my lifetime!
But I'm going to
make it work out.
I'm going to Namek
and that's final!
[YAJIROBE] Hey!
[ALL] Huh? Yajirobe!
That's right! In the flesh.
Korin said to tell you that
Piccolo made it to Namek.
[ALL gasp]
--[CHICHI] What?!
--[ALL] Hmm?
That green guy
with sharp fangs?!
What's so great about that?!
I think you're all
out of your minds!
That does it! I'm taking off!
[ALL gasp]
--[CHICHI] Let go of me!
--[OX-KING] ChiChi, please!
It's too dangerous!
[ALL grunting]
For heaven's sake,
do something!
You're her father,
Ox, think quick!
ChiChi, the
ship's broken!
Remember last time?
[CHICHI] Huh?
[screaming]
[CHICHI sighs]
[CHICHI screaming]
[CHICHI groans]
[ALL sigh]
Please, you don't have
to bow down before me.
But I will say that I amazed
even myself this time. Yep!
It's not what I did,
but how long it took.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the ship is fixed!
[CHICHI gasps]
[ROSHI growls]
[OX-KING &amp; MRS. BRIEF growl]
[OOLONG &amp; PUAR growl]
What...? What's wrong?
I'll tell you what's
wrong, you idiot!
You have the sense of a monkey,
that's what's wrong!
Geniuses! You're all alike!
Hm?! Oh, no you don't!
[ROSHI yells]
[ROSHI] Get back here!
So, trying to sneak
out again, huh?!
Well, this time you're
going to face the music!
This is one battle you're
not going to miss!
[OOLONG] Hey!
She's getting away!
[ROSHI] Oh, no she's not!
--[CHICHI] Hai-yaa!
--[OX-KING] ChiChi, no!
[ROSHI] Oww!
Hmm...
I was thinking and something
just occurred to me.
Yes, it makes sense.
You are the one who defeated
the Ginyu Force, not Vegeta.
Yes, YOU killed
Captain Ginyu.
That's right! Well,
not killed! Changed!
He was blue! Now he's green!
[FRIEZA] Heh. Very funny.
[FRIEZA roars]
[GOKU] Hm?!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Huh?!
Looking for me?
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA grunting]
Huh?!
[thinking] Where is he?!
[GOKU gasps]
[blow lands,
GOKU grunts]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN whimper]
[FRIEZA] Ah, flushed
down the sewer
like the little
rat that he is.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOKU grunting]
[FRIEZA] Heh. You can't
fool me. I know better.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
[thinking] Man, I've got
to think of something.
I'm getting nowhere fast!
Hold on, wait a second...
[GOKU] Huh?
[thinking] Yes! He
can't sense where I am!
He has to see me
with his eyes!
That gives me an idea!
[thinking] It's pretty tricky,
but it can be done.
Oh, man! This is just terrible!
I'm afraid Goku may have
overestimated himself!
Not a chance!
My Dad's gonna tear that
guy to shreds, just watch!
[thinking] Alright! Here goes!
Man, I haven't used this
one in a good while!
[thinking] Kaa... Mee...
Haa.. Mee... Haaaa..!
[thinking] Okay... Don't
move... Stay right there...
Oh, come on. Where are you?
The suspense is
really killing me.
[thinking] Alright...
So far so good!
[thinking] Alrighty, then!
Torpedo number one, away!
[FRIEZA] There he is!
Huh?! Whoa! How rude.
[thinking] Number two, away!
Why you--! Huh?
Trickster!
What?!
Hyaaah!
[FRIEZA grunts]
--Yes!
--[GOHAN laughs]
Oh, man! This... is... nuts!
[GOKU] Wow! Right on!
[GOKU chuckles]
Unbelievable!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laugh]
[BOTH] Yeah!
[FRIEZA] Haaaaa!
[gasping]
[FRIEZA yelling]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Whoa...
Man, this guy's
really something else.
Well, I've got
to hand it to you.
You're the first one
who's ever hurt me,
besides my loving
parents, that is.
Hm... It's been so long
since I've felt pain.
It's such a strange sensation.
What a rare case he is.
Man, is he ticked!
I wouldn't want to be me right
now, but I don't have a choice.
First, I'll have
some fun with him.
Huh...?
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU thinking] Man!
He's doing all this
with his mind!
Hammer time!
[GOKU grunting]
Now! It's my turn!
[GOKU yells]
Mmm!
[GOKU chuckles]
You think
you're so smart!
Huh...?
[FRIEZA grunts]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[FRIEZA cackles]
Oh, man! It's as
big as an island!
No way! How can
he do that?
That thing's gigantic!
Whoa!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Let's see if he
can dodge this one.
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOHAN] Dad, look out!
[PICCOLO] Goku, no!
[GOKU grunts]
[grunting continues]
[FRIEZA giggles]
Here I am!
Ah, no way!
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[thinking] Rrrrgh! I...
can't... budge!
[GOKU grunts]
Here, let ME help.
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA] Gotcha.
You're lucky
I'm so fast.
This ball will go "Boom!" if
it touches anything but me.
[FRIEZA grunts,
GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA] Going somewhere?
[FRIEZA giggles]
Now for the final swat.
This game's over when
you hear the "Bang".
You fiend!
Don't try
to flatter me.
[GOKU yells]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN screams]
Nooo!
[GOHAN screaming]
Thank you, Piccolo!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN coughs]
Huh...?
Oh no!
Wow! What power! And he's
still just warming up!
Huh?!
Frieza could destroy
this whole planet
in an instant if he
wanted to, no problem.
He wasn't serious when
he was fighting Goku,
he was just playing.
Piccolo, if what
you're saying is true,
we're in serious trouble...
My Dad's gone...
Isn't he, Piccolo...?
Nah, not by a
long shot, kid.
Your dad was just
playing as well!
[BOTH] Huh?!
Take a look
over there.
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laugh]
[GOHAN] Alright, Dad!
Man! Shoot!
That was too close for comfort!
I can't make any more mistakes
around this guy, he's too good!
[KRILLIN] Right on!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laugh]
Hmm...?
Amusing little game.
But you're going to have
to find another ball.
How did he do it...?
It's crazy!
He outran the explosion
somehow! That's fast!
It's hard to imagine!
How can they
do all that stuff?
It's... just not normal!
They're monsters...
One good... One evil...
[FRIEZA] I have a
little proposition.
I'd like to ask you
in my native language.
I'm listening.
[FRIEZA speaks in Alien tongue]
It means: "Let's get
down to business."
No more sandbagging.
What d'ya say?
Hmph.
Sounds good! Sure!
[NARRATOR] It seems that
the two super-powers
were merely toying
with each other
But now, Goku and
Frieza have agreed
to lay all their cards
on the table and an
all-out battle between
the two warriors is immanent
on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!