[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z!
Babidi and Majin Buu set their
wicked sights on West City,
and forced
Goku to put his
plans for fusion
training on hold!
[BULMA]
Listen, if we let Majin Buu
get to the West City
and destroy it,
then he'll destroy
the Dragon Radar, Goku!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Yeah, that does pose a problem.
Trunks, listen up. I need
you to go to Capsule Corp
and bring back the radar.
Huh?
[GOKU]
While you do that,
I'll get in front
of Babidi and Majin Buu
and try to slow them down.
Are you sure about that?
Those guys are
pretty tough, you know.
They're going
to wanna fight back.
Yeah, but you let me worry
about them. I'll be okay.
Now, hurry up before
they get ahead of you.
[NARRATOR]
With not a moment to spare,
Trunks raced toward Capsule
Corp at Super Saiyan speed
while Goku put the brakes
on his adversary's advance.
[GOKU]
Hi.
[NARRATOR]
Goku didn't waste any time.
[GOKU]
Here we go!
[yells]
[NARRATOR] The mighty warrior
quickly gathered his strength
to give Majin Buu and
Babidi a lesson in power
they would not soon forget.
[GOKU] And this is what is
known as a Super Saiyan
that has ascended
beyond a Super Saiyan.
[NARRATION] But the
demonstration didn't end there.
[GOKU]
And this...
[NARRATOR]
With a deafening roar,
Goku concentrated his energy
for the transformation
of is life!
Tapping into hidden depths
of his Saiyan powers
that had long lain dormant.
[GOKU yells]
[APE GOKU roars]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] The end result of
this spectacular transformation?
Goku had ascended once again,
achieving an unprecedented
new level of power--
Super Saiyan 3!
[BABIDI whimpers]
Buu!
[NARRATOR] With his newly
energized strength and speed,
Goku launched a dizzying attack
that reduced Majin Buu to
a pudgy pink punching bag.
But after every blow
the Saiyan delivered,
Buu bounced back for more!
How much longer
can Goku hold off
this seemingly
unstoppable monster?
Find out today,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[gasps]
[screams]
[BUU grunting]
Buu, you're supposed
to be winning!
[grunting]
[BABIDI screams]
[PEOPLE gasping, whimpering]
If they keep this up,
they'll destroy our town!
The town? They'll
destroy the whole planet!
Keep it up, Goku!
My dad's stronger than ever!
This is getting dangerous.
Goku may be more
powerful than ever before,
but the harder he fights,
the more Majin Buu's
strength increases!
There seems to be no end to it!
[BUU grunting]
[BOTH grunt]
[gasps]
[laughs]
Ooh, yes!
You have him!
[BABIDI giggles]
[GOKU grunts]
Yes, Majin Buu!
Now squeeze that
Super whatever-he-is
until there's
nothing left of him!
Oh no!
Get outta there!
He'll be alright, Goku's been
in tighter spots than this.
[BABIDI]
C'mon, Buu, finish him off!
Put that oversized
belly of yours to work!
Squeeze the life out of him!
Squeeze! Squeeze!
Turn that blond
freak into spaghetti!
[BABIDI]
What's this?!
[screams]
[GOKU yells]
[BABIDI screams]
[BUU grunts]
Majin Buu!
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS] Grandpa, this is our
third time searching this place!
Could it be somewhere else?!
[DR. BRIEF] Okay, now what
was I looking for again?
What do you two fellows say
we take a little snack break?
I could have pizza bagels
ready in only five minutes!
Don't you get it?!
We can't stop looking!
Majin Buu will destroy West City
along with the Dragon Radar
and without that we won't
be able to bring back
any of the people he's killed,
so we have to keep
it in high gear!
'Kay, hon. So we should
just keep looking?
[BUU grunts]
[BUU grunting]
[BUU giggles]
[BOTH grunt]
Wonderful, Buu! That's great!
[BABIDI gasps]
What a fool!
[thinking]
What's taking Trunks so long?
I can't go on fighting
like this forever.
My energy's draining fast,
and Majin Buu just keeps
coming back for more...
Buu!
[growls]
[BUU]
Buuuuu!
[yells, growls]
[growls]
[BABIDI]
What? Are you leaving so soon?!
Do you think you can just
quit any time you like?!
You're through when
we say you're through!
[BUU]
Hmmmmm!
[SPECTATOR A] Look! That guy's
leading him away from the city!
[SPECTATOR B] All right!
We're gonna be okay!
[growls]
[BUU grunts]
Huh...?
[GOKU grunts]
Good! Perfect, Buu!
Woo-hoo! Woo, woo!
Where did he go?
I can't see him!
[PICCOLO thinking]
Hold on, Goku.
Just a little bit longer.
I can't believe I forgot.
What'd ya say, Bulma?
I'm saying that
Trunks is looking
in the wrong place
for the Dragon Radar!
[BULMA] Sorry, it must've
slipped my mind,
but after we all went to look
for the Dragon Balls earlier,
I left it in the airplane.
[ALL]
What?!
[KRILLIN]
Does Trunks know?!
What'd I just say?
Oh yeah, I know,
but in situations like this
it's really hard for me.
Oh, I just crumble
under pressure!
We have to get in touch
with Trunks immediately.
Krillin, go find
a phone and call him.
I wouldn't know where to start.
I haven't seen a phone
up here in my entire life.
[VIDEL] Hey, I always
carry my phone with me.
Excellent!
I know you guys are
used to relying on
your special powers and all,
but I suggest you look
into technology sometime.
I don't know what
I'd do without it.
Thanks, Videl. I'm gonna
call Trunks right now!
Now, ah, how do
you use this thing?
Ahh, and what would we
have done without you?
[ROSHI grunts]
[BUU grunting]
[BABIDI]
Ha-ha-haaa!
Blast him to smithereens!
[grunts]
[yells]
Darn it, Goku!
What are you doing?!
Are you actually trying
to ignore everything
I've taught you?
If you continue to burn up
your energy like this
your time on Earth will be over!
[BUU laughs]
Amazing, fighting
at this intensity,
and he's still having
the time of his life.
[phone ringing]
Hi, Bulma! How is this beautiful
day treating you, dear?
Uh, great, Mother. Listen, I
need to speak with Trunks now.
He's a little busy,
let me see if I can get him.
Trunks, your
mother's on the phone.
[TRUNKS] Tell her I don't have
time for a pep talk right now!
He says he doesn't have
time for a pep talk.
And I don't have time
for his smart mouth!
You tell him to
get on the phone!
[TRUNKS] For real?
It's in the airplane?!
Oh, thanks a million, Mom!
She said she left
it in the airplane!
Wait, do we even have
an airplane around here?
Help! Help...
So, now you want an airplane.
This is an airplane.
[BUU giggles]
Want to play MORE!
[growls]
--[GOKU growls]
--[BUU grunts]
[chuckles]
[BUU grunts]
Argh!
Kamehameha!
[BUU screams]
[gasps, whimpers]
[BABIDI whimpers] No!
[whimpering continues]
[BABIDI]
No, It can't be.
Not my Buu! My precious Buu!
--[BUU chuckles]
--[GOKU groans]
[BUU squeals]
[giggles]
Do you see now?!
Majin Buu is unstoppable!
[BUU growls]
[gasps]
Not a Kamehameha?
[BUU screams]
[growls, grunts]
[BUU grunts]
[gasps]
[BABIDI grunts]
[BUU giggles]
[whimpering]
[OOLONG yells]
[GOHAN gasps]
[thinking] Father, you must be
fighting one incredible battle.
I can sense it
all the way out here.
Gohan, this may be the one fight
your father
won't be able to win.
[GOHAN gasps]
Majin Buu is just too powerful.
If you want to put
an end to Majin Buu,
you must learn how to
fight with that sword.
You must use it as
an extension of yourself.
That is the only way.
I'll keep trying.
[GOHAN grunts]
[yelps]
[GOHAN]
Wait!
[laughs]
I swear this thing's
getting heavier.
Visualize, Gohan. See the sword
and yourself as a single entity,
one not complete
without the other.
[GOHAN]
Okay.
[GOHAN grunting]
[BUU giggles]
[BABIDI whimpers]
Buu, you bulbous moron!
Are you trying to kill me along
with rest of the planet?!
[growls]
[laughs]
And as for you,
Mr. Would-Be-Super-Hero,
you've done a great job of
protecting this world so far.
Do you have any idea how much
of it you just destroyed?!
[giggles]
Buu, I'm a man of courtesy
as well as strength.
So, I've got to tell you
that I'm quite impressed
by your fighting techniques.
I've fought beings from
beyond nameless galaxies
and you by far are the best.
Thank you!
[DR. BRIEF] Actually,
it's inside this capsule.
Is that what she
was talking about?
Hey, here it is! I found it!
Well, that's
just wonderful, Trunks.
Now, we all have
time for a relaxing lunch.
What is it with you and food?
Gotta go, love ya!
Gosh, I can't believe
he came all this way
and left without
eating anything!
[GOKU thinking]
There he is. Good.
He's on his way back
to the Lookout.
He must've finally
found the Dragon Radar.
I guess it's time to
wrap up my business here
so I can head back, too.
[BOTH]
Huh...?
Hey! Why you go back to normal?
You and me not fight
no more? Buu have fun!
Well, I had a lot of fun, too.
But unfortunately
I have someplace to be
and time won't allow me play
with you all day, Majin Buu.
It's time for
me to say goodbye.
[laughs]
Not likely!
We've been over this!
We'll decide when you leave!
Majin Buu, don't
listen to a word he says!
Get over there and crush him!
[BUU laughs]
All you have to do is brush
this pest out of our way
and then I promise you'll get
your chance to level West City.
That should be more than enough
to lure those three other rats
we're looking for
out of the woodwork.
Hold it, Babidi. Those
three "rats" have names.
Goten, Piccolo, and Trunks.
And I promise,
give them two days
and they'll be ready to fight.
[GOKU] There's no need for
you to destroy West City
or kill anyone else.
They want to fight you.
I'm asking, have some
patience. They'll come to you.
Are they really strong?
Unbelievably.
[BABIDI laughs]
Like it really matters!
Even if we gave them two years
it wouldn't make a difference!
They will never be strong
enough to beat the two of us!
Well, for starters they're
only going to fight one of you
because the other seems to
do nothing but bark orders.
Oh, and Majin Buu I think you
are much too gifted a fighter
to be controlled by
a coward like Babidi!
Bah! Shove it!
See ya.
[gasps]
Huh? Oh? Oh? Ooh...
[whimpers]
Can... you see him?
Did he... Did he just
vanish into thin air?
Buu, you're incompetent!
Don't just stand there floating,
get your doughy pink body moving
and find him right now!
Do you have wax in
your ears, bonehead?!
I am giving you an order!
I am not going to
tell you again, okay!?
You start moving
and you find him!
[BABIDI] Fine, you want
to act like a child?!
Then I'll treat
you like a child!
You have until the
count of three! One, two...
Mister Babidi?
Wha... What is it?
Buu have a better idea.
You're actually
having an idea?
Doesn't that sound
like a great trick?
Okay, then.
Why don't you tell me
what you've come up with
in that walnut-sized
brain of yours?
Buu have a great idea.
You said that already!
Just cough it up so we can
get on with the serious stuff.
Ooohh...
[giggles]
[BABIDI rasps]
[laughs]
[BABIDI grunts]
Now you no talk.
Now no more can say words
to seal Buu back up in ball.
No, no, no!
[BABIDI rasps]
Daddy? Daddy!
Goku.
[GOTEN] You're back!
You were great, Dad!
[PICCOLO]
How are you feeling, Goku?
Fine!
Trunks found the Dragon Radar
and is on his way back!
So we've avoided
one catastrophe, I guess.
Yes, I know. Now, even if Majin
Buu does destroy West City,
we'll be able to
undo all of his damage.
And not only that...
We'll be able to wish back
all of the innocent people
Buu and Babidi killed today.
Every single one of them.
[BABIDI grunts]
You teach me lots
of good things
but Buu think it time
Babidi go bye-bye-bye.
[BABIDI whimpers]
[giggles]
Bye-bye!
[whimpers]
[BUU]
Aaahhh...
[NARRATOR] Now that Babidi is
permanently out of the picture,
Majin Buu is free
to do his own bidding.
But will he continue down
the destructive path
that Babidi has set for him?
And if he does,
is there anyone left
who can stop him?