[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Supremely confident
in his power,
Frieza vowed to defeat Goku
without using his hands!
But, in issuing
himself this challenge,
it soon became clear that
Frieza had bitten off more
than he could chew!
[NARRATOR] Goku continued
to surprise the evil tyrant
with his incredible
strength and blinding speed...
until finally, hard-pressed by
the Saiyan's flurry of attacks,
Frieza was left
with one recourse...
So, I guess you had to
use your hands after all.
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU chuckles]
[FRIEZA giggles]
Okay, from now on,
the deal's off.
[GOKU] Yeah, well, I sort of
gathered that much already!
[FRIEZA] Oh, my! I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I'll bet! Well, don't
go losing any sleep over it.
Shoot! I'm sure that
it was an honest mistake!
Thanks, but no thanks.
[NARRATOR] Now, the time
for games at an end,
the two mighty
warriors square off,
ready to begin the battle anew!
The epic struggle for the fate
of the universe continues today,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[FRIEZA] I really hate
to break this to you,
but I've been holding
back the lion's share
of my power for the
sake of amusement.
But now I'm going
to end this fight.
But before I do, I'd
like to make you an offer:
[GOKU] I'm listening.
[FRIEZA] Join me.
You have so much potential,
it would be a pity
to see it snuffed out
and gone to waste.
What d'ya say?
I can't do it, sorry.
See, I have this nasty
habit of following my heart.
And what does
that get you?
With me you would
live like a god.
Yes, you could have anything.
Or not. You could
choose to suffer and die.
Your call...
No way.
I have everything
that a man could want.
[FRIEZA] Oh-ho-ho, my!
You are so naive.
You know nothing of the
pleasures of this Universe!
Any desire that you have
could be instantly fulfilled!
But have it your way.
Die if you must.
But allow me to let you
in on a little secret.
Hm? What's that?
Well... I haven't even begun
to use my real power yet.
[GOKU] Yeah, well I have
some reserves myself!
Yes, I know.
Five.
Five times what
you've displayed.
Ten at the very most.
But I... I've only used
one percent of my power.
Huh? What? No way!
You're bluffing!
It's just not possible!
Don't be glum.
You should actually
be flattered.
I've never had to summon
this much of my power
to defeat someone.
Fifty percent
of my maximum.
That's all that's
required for this.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOKU growls]
I guess when you
realize this could be
your last fight, there's
no hurry to start.
[GOHAN gasps]
[PICCOLO] No kidding.
We've all experienced
that feeling before.
It's not easy.
But Goku seems to have
a knack for handling
this type of situation.
Do you think my Dad
can pull this one off?
It's hard
to tell, Gohan.
At this point,
both their powers
have gone beyond
our imagination!
That is true...
[GINYU laughing]
[GINYU] Love it!
[laughing continues]
[GINYU grunts]
[GINYU laughs]
[BULMA] Ribbit... Ribbit...
[BULMA thinking]
Who is this monster?!
How could he do this to me?!
I'm going to get him back
if it's the last thing I do!
[GINYU] Well, look
what we have here!
A stow-away, huh?!
Hmm...
This oughta take care
of the toad problem!
[GINYU laughing]
[BULMA screaming]
[thinking] I hate her!
She's obnoxious!
Wicked body-snatcher!
What did I do to deserve this?!
[BULMA sobs]
[BULMA screams]
[GINYU] Whoo-hooo!
[GINYU laughs]
[BULMA thinking] That does it!
Forget this! I can't
take it anymore!
Geronimooo!
[GINYU laughing]
Huh?! Wait-- What're you doing?!
Are you crazy?! I can't see!
[GINYU] Let go of me!
I hate frogs!
What are you doing?!
[PICCOLO] What th--?!
[GINYU screams]
[GINYU] Get off of me!
Whoaaa! I'm too young to die!
[GINYU] Let go of me!
I'm going to kill you!
[PICCOLO] Look out!
[BULMA grunts]
I still got it!
She's still got what?
[KRILLIN] Uhh, hey, Bulma!
What's going on?
I know you're mad at us for
leaving you by yourself,
but it's really not safe
for you to be here.
[GINYU chuckles]
Bulma...?
Are you okay...?
Did you get hit on
the head or something?
[high-pitched GINYU]
Hey, what's that?
That's where Goku and
Frieza are fighting...
[high-pitched GINYU]
Really?! Wow! There they are!
[KRILLIN] Hey! Bulma, no! Wait!
[high-pitched GINYU] Oh, my!
This is fantastic!
[GINYU giggles]
Ooh, yes.
Now I'm stoked.
You're choosing
to die
instead of joining me?
It's a real shame.
[FRIEZA giggles]
Huh?
[FRIEZA] You Saiyans are
really something else.
So proud.
So obstinate.
You're just like Vegeta
and Vegeta's father.
And that radical, Bardock.
You're all alike.
Too stubborn to
recognize a good deal.
Just like moths, rushing
into a flame to die.
But what can I do?
You leave me no other choice.
[FRIEZA] We could have
been so good together...
[high-pitched GINYU] Oh, yeah!
This is going to be one
fabulous show! This is awesome!
[GINYU thinking]
This is strange!
In this body, I can clearly
sense the intensity level
of each of their powers!
Vegeta learned how to
read power levels like this!
[GINYU giggles]
[GINYU] This is great! Ahem..
[high-pitched GINYU]
This is great!
Say what?
[KRILLIN] Are you okay, Bulma?
--[BULMA] Ribbit...
--[GOHAN] Hm?
[BULMA thinking] Oh, please!
[BULMA] Ribbit... Ribbit-Ribbit?
[GOHAN] What's up?
[BULMA thinking]
Oh, Gohan, it's me, Bulma!
Somehow that fiend
managed to steal my body
and now look at me!
It's just awful!
You've got to
help me Gohan!
[high-pitched GINYU]
Enough already!
I want to see some action!
[BULMA thinking]
That's an imposter!
[GOHAN] Hmm...?
Oh, I get it! Yeah!
[BULMA thinking]
Oh, you precious boy!
You really do understand!
You're Captain
Ginyu, right?
[BULMA screams]
You know, it's
not a good idea to
be hanging around here.
Besides, you have a whole
new world to explore!
[BULMA sobs]
[BULMA thinking]
Why me?! This is horrible!
[FRIEZA] I am now at fifty
percent of my maximum.
[FRIEZA] With this
increase, your limitations
will soon become apparent.
Oh, my gosh...
He's not bluffing!
[FRIEZA growls]
Huh?!
[GOKU grunts]
Huh--?
[thinking] This isn't
looking too good.
How can I fight him,
if I can't see him?
[GOKU gasps]
[FRIEZA] My, you're edgy.
I was just scratching my nose.
[GOKU shouts]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
[FRIEZA] Has it become
clear to you yet?
You never had a chance.
I only let you
think you did.
[PICCOLO] Goku!
[GOHAN] Dad, are you alright?
[GOHAN whimpers]
[high-pitched GINYU] Incredible!
Now that's what I call speed!
I can't believe that
I have the priviledge
of watching this fight!
This is monumental!
What a match-up!
Gosh!
This is his greatest
battle ever!
And here I am to witness it!
Bulma, I know the fight
is a big deal and all,
but it's really not a
time to celebrate!
Bulma?
Goku's not faring too
well at the moment.
--[high-pitched GINYU] Oopsie!
--[KRILLIN grunts]
Do me a favor...
After the fight's over
remind me to kill you guys!
[BOTH] Huh?!
[GINYU] Oh!
[high-pitched GINYU giggles]
Well, if she's
threatening us,
that means she's
back to normal.
[KRILLIN sighs]
[GOKU grunts]
[thinking] Man!
How can he be that fast?!
I should at least be
able to follow him!
You should strike. Now,
while my back's turned!
What's wrong?
Don't tell me that the
great Super Saiyan
is throwing in the
towel already?
What a disappointment.
[GOKU growls]
[ROSHI] These things hurt
my toes, they're too small!
[YAJIROBE] Here we go!
I bet it's going to
be all up to me again!
[PUAR] Time to buckle down!
[DR. BRIEF] Lift-off
is in ten minutes.
I'm glad you all
could make it!
Yep! Big day! Wow.
[OOLONG grunts]
[OOLONG] Man! I feel like a
real stud in this spacesuit!
[CHICHI] Alright, guys!
Let's do it!
[DR. BRIEF] I'm cutting
the umbilical cord.
Stand back, everybody.
[DR. BRIEF] If you
have anything to say,
you'd better say it now!
[OX-KING] ChiChi!
You just get Gohan,
and let Goku handle
the fighting!
Do I make myself clear?
[CHICHI] But, Dad,
you don't drink beer!
Bon Voyage, everybody!
Bye-bye! We love you!
[OX-KING] I don't think
she understood me...
[MRS. BRIEF]
Oh, she'll be just fine!
[CHICHI] I've never flown
in outer space before...
My little Gohan is so brave!
Oh, man!
I'm feeling a little
claustrophobic. Oh, no!
[PUAR] Oh, Yamcha, we'll wish
you back somehow. I promise.
Come on! Blast-off!
Before this rabbit's foot
disintegrates!
Alright. This is it.
We're powering up you guys.
[enginge activates]
Forget the suit!
I want out of here!
Oh, man, this
totally stinks!
I'll be good from now on!
I'll change! I swear!
Just help me out
this one last time!
No kidding!
Please! I really
mean it this time!
I promise! For real!
[OOLONG] Would ya shut up?!
You're seriously
freakin' me out!
[ROSHI] Here goes!
Final countdown!
[COMPUTER] Initiating countdown!
Ten... Nine... Eight...
Seven... Six... Five...
--Four... Three... Two...
--No! I can't do it!
--One... Lift off.
--Let me out of here, please!
[engine sputters]
Hm?
Huh?
Hey! Welcome back!
[ALL scream]
[YAJIROBE screams]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU grunts]
Huh...?
What's wrong?
You don't seem to
be having any fun.
Loosen up.
No one likes a sore loser.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA laughs]
It won't be long
now, will it?
But I commend you for
surviving this long.
[KING KAI] Oh, dear!
I'm afraid this
could be it, guys!
He's just too strong!
Yeah, but I bet Goku
is still wearing
his weighted training
clothes, isn't he?
Hmm-mm...
I'm afraid
not, Yamcha.
Goku's giving it
everything he's got.
Wow! This IS serious!
[CHIAOTZU] Goku still has a
chance, doesn't he, King Kai?
[KING KAI] Well, Chiaotzu...
It's not looking too good.
I can tell you that.
[BOTH whimper]
[GOKU growls]
Huh?
Huh?!
Goku...
[TIEN] I wouldn't worry too
much about Goku yet, Chiaotzu!
No sweat...
He's gonna be fine.
[YAMCHA] What?
[TIEN] Don't forget, Goku
still has an ace up his sleeve.
Thanks to you.
Goku hasn't used the
Kaio-Ken Attack yet!
He'll set Frieza
straight when he does!
Right on!
[YAMCHA laughs]
[TIEN] He can still win!
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
[KING KAI] Knock it off!
You're all
being foolish!
[KING KAI] You don't know
what you're talking about!
Goku has been using the Kaio-Ken
Attack the entire time!
But now Frieza is
picking him apart,
even when he's fully
energized by the attack!
I don't know how
long he can last...
We may have to step in,
so stay on your toes!
Come on, Dad!
[high-pitched GINYU giggles]
[high-pitched GINYU]
This is great!
[ALL] Huh?
She's lost it.
[high-pitched GINYU] It looks
like Frieza's going to win
after all!
[high-pitched GINYU giggles]
I should have known!
[PICCOLO] Look!
Shut up or leave!
And that's final!
[high-pitched GINYU] Oh!
[KRILLIN] Are you sure
you're okay, Bulma?
[high-pitched GINYU] Yes!
I guess I got carried
away for a second there...
Sorry, guys!
[BULMA whines]
[KRILLIN &amp; GOHAN] Huh?
Hey!
[high-pitched GINYU]
What's the matter, guys...?
Why are you looking
at me so funny?
You wouldn't hurt a lady,
would you? Hmmmm?!
[GINYU laughs]
Hey! Look out!
It's Ginyu!
[NARRATOR] the situation has
become desperate for Goku!
With the Kaio-Ken Attack
rendered useless by
Frieza, where does
the mighty Saiyan from
Earth go from here?!
it seems that only
a miracle can save him!
And what does the
shameless body-snatcher
Captain Ginyu have in store
for Piccolo and the others?
Find out next time
on Dragonball Z!