[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta decided to
stick to the fighting
and let Goku do the talking.
[GOKU]
We need your energy now!
Raise your hands up!
I beg of you!
[NARRATOR] Many old friends
offered up their energy
when they heard Goku's plea!
But the mass of
humanity didn't join in
until their beloved
champion, Mr. Satan,
asked them to lend a hand!
[CROWD]
Satan! Satan!
[NARRATOR] At last the wall of
skepticism was knocked down
and mankind was freely offering
their collective energy
to help beat the Buu!
[NARRATOR]
Out it poured from the Earth,
arriving like a
flood in Goku's hands.
The Spirit Bomb swelled
to massive proportions!
[GOKU]
Here we go!
[NARRATOR] It was almost
too good to be believed!
Goku finally had what he
needed to defeat Majin Buu.
Just when time
was about to run out,
the mighty Saiyan was
ready to aim and fire!
[GOKU] Here it comes,
Vegeta! Now! Move away!
[KID BUU growls]
Vegeta! Move out of the way!
[VEGETA] Kakarot! What do you
think I'm doing? I can't!
You've got to be kidding...
Vegeta! What are you saying?
You've got to get out of there!
Why are you waiting?!
Fool! Do it!
Fire that thing! Do it now!
[growls]
[VEGETA] Kakarot! Be a true
Saiyan! Launch that Spirit Bomb!
[GOKU]
I can't, Vegeta!
[VEGETA]
You have to!
[chuckles]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot...!
[yells]
Shoot! He knows!
[chuckles]
[DENDE]
This is bad! Very, very bad!
He won't...
He won't fire the bomb!
But... he must!
[CELL] How preposterous! He
would lose just to save Vegeta?
[FRIEZA giggles]
That Saiyan is such a sucker!
[BABIDI] Buu! I hope
you die, you spoiled brat!
[VEGETA groans]
Don't disgrace our efforts
with your sentimental rubbish!
Launch the bomb!
[GOKU] No! You're the one
who got us this far!
[KID BUU chuckles]
[laughs]
[KID BUU growls]
[KID BUU chuckles]
--[gasps]
--[chuckles]
[laughs]
Vegeta!
Darn him!
Buu...?
Buu! You're alive!
I thought you were dead!
Oh, Buu! It's so good to see ya!
[MR. SATAN grunts]
[MR. SATAN]
Ow...
Buu? A-Are you all right?
Oh, boy! Is he mad!
[GOKU grunts]
[KING KAI] I don't believe
this is happening!
Goku! This doesn't
make any sense!
Vegeta wants you to do it!
Please! Launch the bomb! Now!
[KID BUU snarls]
[GOKU gasps]
Aaah! Darn you!
[yells]
What a mess...
Vegeta! Forgive me!
I can't do it!
[KID BUU chuckles]
[yells]
[BUU shrieks]
[KID BUU gasps]
Get him!
[MR. SATAN]
Hey! But you already have him!
Oh! I see! Right!
[BOTH BUUS growl]
[BUU yelps]
Please, don't die, Buu!
Hey, you! What are you
waiting for?! It's now or never!
[GOKU thinking]
He's got Vegeta!
Way to go, Champ!
You really are a hero!
[snarls]
[GOKU]
This is for you, Majin Buu!
It's from the people of Earth!
Spirit Bomb!
[growls]
[screams]
Yaaagh!
What?! No!
[KID BUU growls]
[grunting]
[GOKU]
Come on! Go!
Go!!
[KID BUU yells]
[GOKU]
It won't budge!
[PICCOLO using ESP]
Gohan! Can you hear me?
[GOHAN using ESP]
Piccolo! Piccolo, you feel that?
My Dad and Majin Buu!
This is it!
[PICCOLO using ESP]
You got that right.
They appear to be fighting in
the Sacred World of the Kais.
[GOHAN using ESP]
Yeah, you're right.
[GOHAN using ESP] And we
can't even get there to help
unless Kibito Kai takes us.
[PICCOLO using ESP]
Yeah, that's true.
But we can sense
the fight a lot better
if we go back to the Lookout.
[GOHAN using ESP]
Cool! Meet you there!
[PICCOLO using ESP]
Sounds good.
Goten! Trunks! It's time to go!
[BOTH grunting]
[yells]
Ah! No way!
Rrgh! I know you're
stronger than me, Buu,
but this is more than just
my power. It's everyone's!
So I can not
and will not lose!
[MARON] Why can't we
see the fight, Mommy?
[ANDROID 18] Because it's in
another world, sweetheart.
It's Piccolo!
[YAMCHA]
All right, Piccolo!
[ROSHI]
It's good to see you, Piccolo!
[PICCOLO]
Likewise!
[CHICHI]
Huh? Gohan!
Gohan...?
[VIDEL] I was worried sick
about you, you idiot!
[VIDEL sobs]
Gosh, Videl! I really
wish you wouldn't cry...
Yeah! Me, too! He's my son! I
should be crying! How dare you!
Easy there, ChiChi! Face it:
your son's growing up.
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Hi, Mom!
[GOTEN laughs]
[BOTH sniff]
Trunks!
Goten! Aww...
[PICCOLO thinking]
Something's not right!
Goku's power's decreasing!
Why are you dragging your feet,
Kakarot?! Finish the job!
Darn it! I'm out of power!!
Oh, no! Please! Not now!
Don't give out on me now!
No! No! No! Look!
He's losing ground!
He can't do it.
We overestimated his strength!
He's totally drained!
[KID BUU laughs]
No! Hold on!
[NAMEKIAN A]
I feel faint...
[NAMEKIAN B]
Me, too...
It's no good! Look!
He's falling back!
The Spirit Bomb's
not strong enough!
He needs more "Umph!"
More energy!
Yes, but how?!
We've already given him
everything we've got!
How can someone
be that strong?!
Look! He's taking control!
Geez! This is a
rip off! Come on!
You'd better beat him, Goku!
I didn't get extended cable
to see you lose!
[yells]
[KID BUU grunts]
[chuckles]
[VEGETA]
He's maxed out!
Dende! Can you hear me?
We need you! Come here now
and heal Kakarot!
It's now or never!
There's no time left!
Sir, Vegeta's right.
I can help Goku if I go.
Yes. No doubt...
But I've given
up too much energy.
Instant Transmission
won't work now. I'm sorry.
What? Oh no...
[DENDE] Vegeta! Our power
levels are too depleted.
We don't have enough
energy to make the jump.
Great! What are
we supposed to do?!
Hey! It's in your hands!
We need more energy from
the Earth! Talk to your people!
[VEGETA]
If we can't strengthen Kakarot,
then our only chance is to
strengthen the Spirit Bomb!
Now talk!
No! Wait! Vegeta! Don't do it!
[KING KAI] We've already taken
the maximum amount of energy
from the Earthlings!
They haven't had
time to recover yet!
[groaning]
Hey, Mr. Sandwich,
I'm Fa-Fa-Farmer!
[KING KAI]
If we take anymore
we'll be drawing on
their vital life force--
the energy that
they need to live on.
If they give more energy
right now, they'll all die!
You old fool! Quiet!
Just think of the alternative.
You know we don't
have any other choice!
Now talk! Tell them we
need more energy! More energy!
But, I-I-I-I...
I-I c-cant!
[VEGETA] Then the whole
Universe is going to die!
[growls]
Please! Not now!
Don't let me give out now!
Maybe you're right! Maybe it is
the right thing to do!
No way! Don't you give in!
Please forgive me, but I can't!
I can't! It would destroy me!
What do you mean?
I've been a shameless fake
my whole life!
But they believe me!
They love me!
So if I turn my back on them
now, what will it make me?
[MR. SATAN]
Not even I can sink that low!
I-It would be worse than
death to betray them like that!
[sobs]
Hey! Listen!
I'm the one who had
Dende wish the Earthlings
and their planet back to life.
If it wasn't for me,
they'd still all
be dead right now!
[VEGETA]
Wait a second!
We still have
a wish, don't we?
[gasping]
Yes! Of course!
Porunga is still
with us, Vegeta!
And he's been very patient!
What is your wish! You have
kept me waiting long enough!
Uhh! Yes, Porunga! Can you
bring the power level of Goku,
the Saiyan who is fighting Majin
Buu on the Kai Planet right now,
back to normal?
Such a wish is well
within my power to grant!
Cool! Porunga...
[speaks in Namekian]
Okay!
[laughing, cheering]
It's no use! I can't...
[KID BUU cackles]
[KID BUU shrieks]
[DENDE]
Goku! We used the third wish
to restore your
power back to normal!
[GOKU] Hey! You're right!
Whoo-hoo! It's back!
Thank you!
Thank you, guys... Wow.
[GOKU yells]
[yells]
[KID BUU growls]
[DENDE]
He's doing it! All right!
[NAMEKIANS laughing, chattering]
I taught him that technique!
That a boy!
[laughs]
Hey guys, you feel that?
[GOTEN]
Is that my Dad?
Yes! He has his
old strength back!
[FRIEZA thinking]
Hmph! Why am I not surprised?
[BABIDI] This must be
what joy feels like!
[KID BUU grunts]
[growling]
[GOKU] It looks like it's
the end of the road, Buu!
It's a darn shame!
[GOKU] When I first met you,
I could sense that
there was good in you.
You were like a
naughty little child
that didn't know any better.
FIghting was more of a game
than anything else.
[GOKU] But then you seperated.
The evil was expelled--
The struggle taking place inside
of you was now on the outside
for all to see.
And the darkness
overpowered the light.
[GOKU] After that,
you were different.
You were ruthless.
You became a living nightmare
and you delighted
in every moment of it.
Didn't even show a
shred of decency or mercy!
And that's why
it has to end like this.
You'll have to
learn the hard way,
and know what it feels like
to have YOUR life
taken away against YOUR will!
It's wrong!
Maybe you'll come back some day.
As... As a better person,
I hope. I'd like that.
Perhaps we'll have
a little one-on-one!
[KID BUU grunts]
Adios!
I'll be waiting
for you, Majin Buu!
[KID BUU squeals]
--[DENDE] Goku!
--Kakarot!
--[GOHAN] Father!
--Goku!
[ALL]
Do it!
Haaaa!!
[KID BUU screams]
[screams]
It's over...
It's about time.
[whimpers]
[GOKU] We make a pretty good
team after all, don't we?
[GOKU chuckles]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[BOTH laugh]
[NARRATOR]
Two Saiyan rivals, now friends,
have prevailed
against all odds.
Majin Buu is gone.
But true victory
could not have been won
without the help from
every being on Earth.