[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Arqua from the East Quadrant
started his fight against Goku
by transforming the arena
into a whirl-pooling aquarium.
[NARRATOR] Deep in the water
and deep into trouble,
Goku was unable to match
the finned fighter's
underwater speed.
[GOKU] Solar Flare!
[NARRATOR] But with the help
of the Solar Flare technique,
Goku managed to blind Arqua long
enough to escape into the air.
[NARRATOR] Wasting no time, Goku
used his most trusted attack:
The Kamehameha Wave.
[GOKU] Haaa!
[NARRATOR]
And Goku's fishy foe
was blown right
out of the water.
[ARQUA screams]
[grunts]
[NARRATOR] But the fighting
was far from over.
Next on the mat:
Pikkon vs. Olibu!
The most anticipated
match of the tournament.
Both fighters had been training
for centuries for this chance.
Both boasted incredible
skill and strength.
Both were hoping
to win the gold.
But only one would
stay standing...
[MUSHROOM MC]
It's official, people!
Pikkon haaas won!
[NARRATOR]
The battle between giants
has been fought to its end.
Olibu is out.
Now, if Goku wants to
win the tournament,
he'll have to get past Pikkon.
[GOKU] Gee... Beating Pikkon
is gonna take all I've got...
[CROWD roars]
Yeah! Goku!
Make mince meat out of him!
Maraikoh! I know you're
not from my quadrant
but I want you to
pound that rookie!
It's quite something that our
newcomer has come this far...
[WINGED MAN] Hmph. You know he
won't make it through this bout.
No, there's something
about his energy--
he may be the first person
from the North Quadrant
to earn the
Grand Kai's lesson...
You're dreaming...
And who says the dead
don't know how to party?!
Well, what do you say we move
right on to the first match
of the semifinals!
Maraikoh from the West...
And Goku from the North!
C'mon, people, let's do this!
[gong crash]
[CROWD cheers]
--[MARAIKOH yells]
--[GOKU yells]
[MARAIKOH laughs]
[GOKU yells]
[laughing continues]
[BOTH growl]
[GOKU yells]
[thinking] He dodges well...
but lacks focus...
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU squeals]
[MARAIKOH] Haah!
[KAIS gasp]
Oh! Just look at that hit!
Goku's been knocked into orbit!
He better watch out
for those meteors!
--[GOKU groans]
--Whoops!
[GOKU grunts]
[MARAIKOH laughs]
[MARAIKOH growls]
Huh?!
So he wants more, eh?
Well, I'll give him somethin'...
[MARAIKOH growls]
[laughing]
Huh? Uh, oh!
Oh, wait a second...
Yeah, I'll give it to him...
As soon as I stop
spinning. Hold on...
Maraikoh!
Goku!
[MARAIOH growls]
[yells]
[BOTH whimper]
[MUSHROOM MC] Goku is landing!
But where's Maraikoh?
[CROWD murmurs]
[GOKU thinking]
He's hidden himself...
But I can just barely
sense his energy...
[GOKU thinking] He's... there!
[GOKU yells]
[MARAIKOH whimpers]
[GOKU grunts]
[BOTH whimper]
He's knocked out
and out of the ring!
You can't lose worse
than that, folks!
Goku has won!
--Yes! Ha, ha, ha!
--[CROWD cheers]
Well, I never doubted him!
Not even once!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Alright! Yeah!
[GRAND KAI laughs]
[GRAND KAI] Yeah.
[PIKKON thinking] He shows
more strength with every fight.
He's just playing
with his opponents.
[GOKU laughs]
[PIKKON thinking] I look
forward to ending his game.
Wow... Maraikoh sure
got his tail whooped!
His coach must be a loser.
Oh yeah, that's right, West Kai.
He's from your quadrant, huh?
He threw the fight...
[KING KAI growls]
I told him to since it'd be
kinda rude for both my fighters
to be in the final round.
[KING KAI screams]
[WEST KAI]
That's right, blue boy!
So you better get all that
stupid victory dancing
out of your system,
because there's no way
Goku's gonna beat my Pikkon!
[WEST KAI chuckles]
Can't you ever lose a match
without giving some lame excuse?
Goku's going to win this
tournament and that's final!
No, Pikkon is going to win it!
Goku!
Pikkon!
--Goku!
--Pikkon!
[yelling continues]
[BOTH growl]
[GRAND KAI laughs]
This is silly.
Let's just make a bet.
A bet?
To make things more interesting.
If Goku beats Pikkon, then I'll
give you my West Kai planet.
You'll give me your planet?!
Yeah...
Now it's your turn.
You have to bet me something.
Well, if Pikkon wins,
I'll give you my planet...
Oh, I forgot... It blew up...
[WEST KAI] Hmmm...?
--Uuhhh...
--[WEST KAI growls]
If you want to wimp out
it's not too late...
I am not a wimp!
In fact, I am so confident
in Goku's abilities
that I'll become your servant
if Pikkon beats him!
Aaaagreed!
I'm betting my home and
you're betting your freedom!
Now you better not
back out of this!
'Cause I'm gonna have plenty
of chores for you to do!
Oh, please.
I back up what I say!
Heeey!
We were just talking
about you, Goku!
Great fight!
[GOKU groans]
What? What's wrong?
[intense growling]
--[gasping]
--[KING KAI] Goku!
--[growling continues]
--What's that noise?!
It's my stomach growling.
[yelping]
[GRAND KAI laughs]
[GRAND KAI] I can say
this about you, Goku:
You tell it like it is!
My cooks have made some
killer dishes for you!
So pig on out!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] Oh, you're not kidding!
Thanks, Grand Kai!
I'm just dying of hunger!
Wait! Goku!
[squealing]
[GOKU] What, King Kai?
He said I could!
Hey, I know you're
hungry and all...
But don't you need to
watch this next fight?
[CROWD roars]
[GOKU] Nah... It's
not important!
Not important?!
Huh...? Hey!
You better watch
your mouth, boy!
Hmph.
It's not important 'cause I
already know who's gonna win!
What? Are... you psychic?
I... wanna know...
[GOKU]
I'll tell you in a minute!
First is food! Oh, wow!
[GRAND KAI laughs]
[panting]
Pick up the speed,
you jelly rolls!
Not one of you boys even
made it the semifinals!
Do you know how
embarrassed that makes me?!
Now you better get
those pedals moving
or you'll be running one
MILLION more laps!
I'm the queen,
you hear me?!
And queens should win the GOLD!
[doors creak]
[CROWD cheering]
[GOKU chomping, slurping]
[TORBIE yells]
[CHEF gasps]
--[CHEFS whimper]
--[TORBIE screams]
[GOKU] More please!
[screaming continues]
[MUSHROOM MC] Well,
that's it folks!
Whatever's left of Torbie
has definitely been defeated!
[CROWD cheers]
[WEST KAI laughs]
Alright!
Here we are at the final
matchup of the tournament!
[CROWD cheers]
Competing for gold from
the West Quadrant...
It's Pikkon!
[CROWD cheers]
And fighting against him
from the North Quadrant...
The rookie wonder Goku!
[MUSHROOM MC] Um, hello?
Okay, would all Gokus
please report to the arena?
--Your fighter is waiting...
--That's enough!
You can finish your meal
just as soon as you beat
the stuffing out of Pikkon!
Let's go!
[MUSHROOM MC] Well, folks
it seems like our contender's
having somewhat
of a lunch break.
[WEST KAI] Oh, this
boy is making me sick!
[GOKU] Wait, King Kai!
Let me have one more bite!
Come on!
[PIKKON] He's either
a fighting genius...
or a total fool...
[panting]
[EAST KAI] Come on, boys!
Feel the burn!
Whoa!
The finals...
You boys better keep
up the running!
We're on the honor system here!
[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC] And now,
may the best one win!
[gong crash]
[GOKU yells]
[blows landing]
I know you're fast enough
to block those hits...
[PIKKON chuckles]
It's because those punches
of mine weren't strong enough
to hurt you, is that it?
Well, you'd better
start blocking
when I use my real strength.
[PIKKON] No games!
[GOKU grunts]
[PIKKON grunts]
[PIKKON yells]
[PIKKON gasps]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU thinking] There's
only one way to shake this...
[PIKKON chuckles]
[BOTH grunt]
[KAIS grunting]
[GRAND KAI grunting]
[GRAND KAI thinking] Hmmm...
Now that's more like it!
[PIKKON growls]
[BOTH grunt]
[growling]
[PIKKON gasps]
[shoes squealing]
[growling continues]
Oh, pull yourself
together, Pikkon!
For Pete's sake!
That a boy, Goku!
Push him right out!
[growling,
shoes squealing]
[GRAND KAI thinking]
Looky-looky!
These kids are
something to watch!
[shoes squealing]
[GOKU chuckles]
So... is this that
"real strength"
you were talking about?
What?!
[PIKKON] Or do you still think
you're just playing with me?
[GOKU grunts]
[growling]
[PIKKON thinking]
Why can't I push him back?
[GOKU growls]
[thinking] I know he can't
be stronger than me...
[PIKKON yells]
[GOKU shouts]
[GOKU chuckles]
You're much stronger
than I thought, Goku.
Thanks, Pikkon...
You're not too bad
a fighter yourself.
Hmph.
Uh?
[MUSHROOM MC] Ho-ho man!
I've never seen this
side of Pikkon before!
Just what is he up to?
[GOKU gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
[GOKU grunts]
Huh...?
This stuff must
weigh a ton!
Okay. I get it.
You wear this heavy stuff
to help you train.
I should introduce you
sometime to my friend Piccolo.
Hmm...? Piccolo?
[GOKU] Yeah! He wears
weighted training clothes too.
You guys would get along great!
[KAIS whimper]
[crashing]
[GRAND KAI chuckles]
[thinking] Hmph!
This should be good...
Now I've got a trick.
[GOKU yells]
I didn't know it was going
to be that kind of fight.
[PIKKON chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Well, well.
It seems both fighters
have been keeping
a few secrets.
With his heavy
training robe removed,
just how great will
Pikkon's true strength be?
And with Goku's upgrade to Super
Saiyan,
you can count on this battle
to be pretty extreme.
The tournament can
have only one winner.
Who will it be?