[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Krillin stepped into the
ring to show his stuff
in the World Martial
Arts Tournament.
His opponent had the
pounds to throw around,
but a well-placed punch
knocked the wind
out of the overweight warrior.
From there, a slap-kick
combination assured
an easy victory for Krillin.
[PINTAR grunting]
[NARRATOR] The stage was set
for the second bout to begin!
But before the
fighting could start,
Piccolo made a
shocking discovery
about his mysterious
opponent, Shin.
[PICCOLO thinking]
Why would he be here?!
I promise you'll know soon.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[SHIN thinking]
You'll know soon.
[PICCOLO] I'm sorry.
I can't...
[GOHAN] He's quitting?
[NARRATOR] That's right!
To everyone's surprise,
Piccolo withdrew from the match
and left the ring before
a single punch was thrown.
[SHIN] Perhaps he knows more
about me than I thought...
[NARRATOR] Despite this
unusual turn of events,
the competition continued.
To thunderous applause, Gohan's
feisty girlfriend Videl
and her opponent Spopovitch
entered the stadium.
Even though they differ in size,
Videl is heavily favored
to win the match.
However, this suspicious glance
Shin gave Spopovitch
as they passed seems to
suggest that there's more
to the bald-headed brute
than meets the eye.
What is it that Shin knows
about Spopovitch?
And how will it
affect the outcome
of his battle with Videl?
Find out today!
[CROWD] Videl! Videl! Videl!
[chanting continues]
[SPOPOVITCH snarls]
[SPOPOVITCH growling]
[VIDEL] Hmph.
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[VIDEL thinking]
Ugh... What a freak!
[SPOPOVITCH snarls]
This guy really wants to fight!
Huh?
[PICCOLO thinking] It must
be him... I'm sure of it!
Videl! Go get 'em!
Heh...
I betcha this guy doesn't
even make it five seconds.
[COPS] Videl! Videl!
You're the one! Videl!
Sounds like Gohan's girlfriend
has quite a few fans up there.
Sure does...
What? Gohan's girlfriend?
Hah! That kid! He's
a chip off the old block! Yup!
Yeah! And did you know?
Videl comes from
a very wealthy family!
She's a perfect match for Gohan!
Sure, if you overlook the fact
that Mr. Satan's her dad...
[YAMCHA laughs]
Hey, Mr. Satan is her dad?! Well
that makes things interesting!
[SPOPOVITCH growling]
[growling continues]
Hey, sports fans!
Are you ready?!
It's Videl versus
Spopovitch! Here we go!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[CROWD cheering]
[PICCOLO thinking] If it
had been anyone else,
ANYONE else, I would NOT have
thrown the match...
[SHIN] Hmph. What is it?
Forgive me if I'm mistaken...
but I have to ask you...
Yes...?
Well, are you...
Are you the Grand Kai?!
Sorry. No, I'm not.
I'll tell you who he is.
The Supreme Kai!
[PICCOLO gasps]
Supreme Kai?!
[VIDEL yells]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[VIDEL] Hyah!
Alright!
Videl is on the attack!
She's really giving it
to Spopovitch!
Look at that incredible
technique! What a fighter!
[VIDEL yells]
[PICCOLO whimpers]
Keep that information
to yourself, please.
I don't want the others
to know just yet.
Enjoy the competition, Piccolo.
[SUPREME KAI chuckles]
So... The Supreme Kai!
[PICCOLO] I know of the four
Kais who watch over the universe
and the Grand Kai who
oversees their actions.
I've always suspected that there
was an even greater Kai
above the Grand Kai,
but I never knew for sure.
The Supreme Kai... Hmmm?
What is he doing here on Earth?
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO] And why is he so
interested in fighting Goku?!
What's up, Piccolo?
What did that
Shin guy say to you?
[PICCOLO gasps]
He wasn't rude, was he?
You want me to set him
straight for you?
I bet if I told him you were
once the guardian of Earth,
he'd have a little more respect!
[PICCOLO gasps]
No, don't do that! Please!
Don't do anything!
Please don't!
[GOKU gasps]
[KING KAI] Oh my!
That kid can't really be
the Supreme Kai?!
Can he?!
[thinking] Even I've never
actually seen him before...
So why has he entered the World
Martial Arts Competition?!
--[VIDEL] Hyah!
--[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] Spopovitch is down!
And from the looks of it,
he's down for good!
I'll start the count!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[HAT TEEN] Whoa!
[SPOPOVITCH snarls]
[VIDEL growls]
It's incredible!
Spopovitch is up again!
What an amazing athlete!
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[VIDEL grunts]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[VIDEL yells]
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[CROWD cheering]
[KILLA talks incoherently]
Spopovitch cannot
fight like that.
I don't know.
He's changed so much
since the last time he fought.
Yeah!
[SPOPOVITCH laughs]
[KILLA talks incoherently]
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[VIDEL growls, yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[VIDEL grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[VIDEL gasps]
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[VIDEL growls]
[ANNOUNCER] Videl has done some
serious damage to her opponent,
but it looks like Spopovitch is
not about to give up so easily!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[VIDEL grunts]
[VIDEL grunts,
SPOPOVITCH yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Spopovitch
is down again! No wait!
He's getting up!
[VIDEL] Agh!
[ANNOUNCER] How does he do it?!
[SPOPOVITCH snarls]
[VIDEL growls]
[BOTH grunt]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[GOKU]
How's she doing out there?
She's kicking butt!
Yeah! Videl is really
wearing this guy down!
I give him
two more minutes, tops!
Ah! This is a just
waste of my time.
[VIDEL yells,
SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[VIDEL yells]
[SPOPOVITCH grunting]
[ANNOUNCER] And Spopovitch
takes another fall!
I think you'll all agree
that young Videl
really packs a punch!
Looks like she may have
put an end to this one!
What an incredible fight!
Yeah Videl!
Keep it up, girl!
Videl will make a
great wife for Gohan!
Yeah!
And it looks like she won't have
any problem keeping him in line!
So you agree!
I knew that you would!
We've got to get
those two married!
[CHICHI laughs]
[BULMA laughs]
Hold on! Has Gohan
even met Mr. Satan yet?
See! I told you she would win!
Huh...?
[CROWD gasping]
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
You're kidding!
[GOKU growls]
[ANNOUNCER]
How about that, folks?
Spopovitch is up once again!
Is this guy tough or what?
Whoaa!
[VIDEL thinking] Doesn't
he know when to give up?!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[GOKU thinking]
I don't know what it is,
but something's
not right here...
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[ANNOUNCER] No matter
how hard Videl tries,
she just can't stop Spopovitch!
That's right! He just
won't stay down! Yes!
He's going to go the distance!
This is hand-to-hand
combat at its best!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[SPOPOVITCH growling]
Time to end this...
Now!
[VIDEL growls]
[VIDEL yells]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH grunting]
[VIDEL yells]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
Yeah! Nice one!
[grunting continues]
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[VIDEL grunts]
He's down!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] That could be it!
Videl may have
just won this match
with that brilliant maneuver!
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[CROWD gapsing]
Huh...?
Ahh...
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
Wow? He's up.
What's going on?!
She should quit
the match, now...
Something's not right
about him...
Wha--?!
Forfeit? Why?
But Videl's got
the advantage, Goku!
[GOHAN] Yeah, Dad!
Krillin's right!
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[VIDEL growls]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts,
VIDEL yells]
No!
[VIDEL grunts]
[ERASA gasps]
Oh, Videl!
Ah! She's okay!
I'm sure she can take
a whole lot more than that!
Hey, get up! Come on!
I won't let you marry Gohan
if you don't get up now!
I sure wouldn't want ChiChi as
my mother-in-law, would you?
Uh, no...
[VIDEL grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[VIDEL gasps]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts,
VIDEL screams]
She's done for!
Oh no!
Ah--!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[CROWD gasping]
Uh? Ah!
[VIDEL growls]
Look! Videl is above the ring!
Floating in the air!
It's amazing!
[VIDEL growls]
You see that?
I think so!
[GOHAN] Thatta girl! Ya know,
I taught her that little trick.
I think she would
have been better off
if she had fallen out
of the ring...
[GOHAN] Why?
There's something very
unusual about Spopovitch...
Look at him.
There's no way he could
withstand all of Videl's attacks
and still continue to fight!
[GOHAN] Then how does he do it?
What's his secret?
[GOKU] I don't know, Gohan...
But I'm going to find out!
[MR. SATAN] What? How can Videl
be losing to Spopovitch?!
It's true...
[MR. SATAN laughs]
No, that can't be right!
I finished Spopovitch
in the first round
and I know for a fact
that my daughter
is much stronger than him!
After all, let's not forget
I taught her everything
she knows, so she'll be fine!
Yes, of course, sir,
but he seems to be a
lot stronger than before!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
No, he's not! He's weak!
Videl is just toying with him.
She's trying to make the match
a little more exciting
for the crowd, that's all!
Are you sure?
I think I know
my own daughter!
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[VIDEL growls]
[VIDEL grunts]
Huh--?
[VIDEL gasps]
What the--?!
[SPOPOVITCH rasps]
[ANNOUNCER] Spopovitch's head
has spun completely around!
[rasping continues]
[VIDEL whimpers]
Oh, she didn't...
Oh man! Yup!
He's down for good!
[ERASA gasps]
Wow!
[BOTH whimper]
--[MARRON gasps]
--No! Don't look!
Well...
That's it! Videl has clearly
beaten her opponent.
But I'm afraid
she will be disqualified
for using excessive force.
Those are the rules.
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[VIDEL gasps,
CROWD gasps]
[grunting continues]
[CROWD murmuring]
[VIDEL] Ahh...?
[GOHAN gasps]
He's alive!
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH grunting,
bones creaking]
[VIDEL gasps]
[SPOPIVITCH snarls]
[VIDEL whimpers]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Gah! Guh! Ah!
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] I don't know
how to explain this,
but somehow Spopovitch has
pulled himself together!
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
Who is... this guy?!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[GOHAN gasps]
[SPOPOVITCH laughs]
Whoa! Goku was right!
Videl should have forfeited!
Oh, this guy is
definitely not normal!
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
--Rrgh?!
--[ANNOUNCER] Ahh!
Videl has once again out
maneuvered her opponent
by taking to the air!
Yeah! That's it!
You just stay up there, Videl,
'til you get your strength back!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[chuckling]
He's flying!
No, he can't?!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[NARRATOR] Videl has
no place left to hide
now that Spopovitch
has taken flight.
The bald-headed brute
refuses to give up
and he's determined
to clip Videl's wings
and win the match.
What is the secret to
his unstoppable power?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!