[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
The evil Dodoria made his
presence felt on Planet Namek.
With ruthless precision,
he unleashed his wrath
on all who dared
oppose him!
And as the
rampage continued,
one thing became
painfully clear,
old or young,
none would be spared!
Gohan watched the
gruesome events unfold
until finally, he
could watch no more!
Stop it!!
[NARRATOR] The young warrior
sprang into action,
and brought Dodoria's spree
of terror crashing to a halt!
If you want him, you're
gonna have to get through me!
C'mon, Gohan! We gotta
get outta here! Right now!
[NARRATOR] But unfortunately,
this was only the beginning
of our heroes' troubles.
I must find out who those
little rodents are.
[NARRATOR] Soon, Dodoria
was in hot pursuit...
Gohan!
[NARRATOR] And Krillin
had to risk it all,
in an effort to
slow him down!
[KRILLIN] All right, big guy,
watch the birdie!
Solar Flare!
[DODORIA grunting]
[DODORIA] Ugh!
My eyes! My eyes!
[NARRATOR] Has the gamble
truly paid off?
Whadda you know?
It actually worked!
[NARRATOR]
Stay tuned!
[DODORIA growling]
Oh, they're dead!
[DODORIA]
They're close. I know it.
I can practically
smell them!
Huh. How 'bout that?
He flew right past us.
He's not gonna find us
without his scouter.
We just need to lay low
until he decides to give up.
Who knows?
With a little luck,
we might just get out
of this in one piece!
Bah! This is pointless.
Where are they?
I don't have time to
search this whole canyon.
You were right, Krillin.
Look, he's leaving!
Heh. Look what
I found here!
[ALL whimpering]
Aahh...
Haah!
[KRILLIN screaming]
[DODORIA chuckles]
[chuckling continues]
Ha! There you go. Let's see you
little insects hide from that!
[DODORIA laughs]
There's no way
they survived.
Frieza should be pleased.
At least I hope.
He did say he wanted
to know who they were.
[DODORIA]
But who cares?
After all, it doesn't
matter who they were,
they're dead now!
[DODORIA laughs]
[GOHAN] That was close...
[KRILLIN sighs]
No kidding. Now, c'mon.
Let's get back to Bulma.
Uh... Hey, can you fly?
Oh. Well, yes.
Actually, I'm
still learning.
[KRILLIN laughs]
Oh, and thanks a
lot for saving me.
No, don't thank me. Gohan's the
one who charged in to get you.
I just followed
his lead.
Thanks, but, that's
not true, Krillin.
If it weren't for you, that guy
woulda caught us for sure!
[KRILLIN laughs sheepishly]
So, anyway, why don't
you just stick with us?
I promise, we're nowhere near
as bad as those other jerks.
[gasps]
I don't...
[BOTH laughing]
Well, uh... yeah!
[GOHAN] Great! Just
follow us. It's that way.
[BULMA] So, we're still trying
to get the Dragon Balls,
but we found out
there's this group
of creepy aliens here
looking for them, too.
I don't know
who they are,
but they've already
got four of them!
And if they
get all seven...
Well, it's like,
what's the point
of even coming here
in the first place?
I mean, it's not fair
if I have to suffer
all this hardship
for nothing!
Hello? Dad!
Are you listening?!
[DR. BRIEF] Oh, uh, o-of
course, dear. Of course...
Yes, that sounds
just terrible.
I know, and that's
not the half of it.
See, a couple of those
creepy alien guys
I'm talking about
blew up our ship!
So, I don't know how we're
gonna get back to Earth.
It looks like
we're stuck here!
[DR. BRIEF] Hmm...
Stuck on Namek, eh?
Well, now,
that's no good.
But, I wouldn't
worry, dear.
Goku is on his way there in
another ship, even as we speak.
I'm sure you and the boys can
catch a ride home with him.
What? You mean Goku's on his
way here? To Planet Namek?
That's great!
Oh, Daddy, we're saved!
[DR. BRIEF] Yes, I
thought you'd like that.
He should be there in,
oh... about six days.
[BULMA giggling]
Goku! Yaay!
[DR. BRIEF] But, I'm afraid
it's not all good news.
There's still one
thing that worries me.
Ah! Uh-oh...
Um, Dad?
[DR. BRIEF] The ride home might
be a bit rough on everyone.
Goku took the ship
before I could install
the cappuccino
machine!
[GOKU grunting]
Ah... Now let's see what
we've got in this refrigerator!
After all
this training,
I'd say I've
earned a little snack.
Aahh...
Uhh...
What, is that
all there is?
Oh well, I guess it'll
have to do as an appetizer.
Alright, let's see...
This... this... that too...
[GOKU giggling]
Phew! Yeah!
That hit the spot!
Aahh...
[GOKU yelling]
Oh, I guess I forgot to
turn off the gravity machine.
Bah. It's gonna take
much longer to find
the last two Dragon Balls
without our scouters.
And this planet...
It all looks the same to me.
We should just blow the whole
thing up and be done with it.
Huh...? Aaugh!
[DODORIA grunting]
Huh?
[VEGETA laughing]
Y-You!
Vegeta!
It's been a long time,
Dodoria. How are you?
Rrgh... I
should've known.
Shooting people in the
back always was your style.
Careful now.
We're all alone.
Frieza and Zarbon
aren't here to back you up.
I'd watch what I
said if I were you.
[DODORIA growls]
Then again, I suppose
it doesn't matter.
I'm still going to
kill you either way.
[chuckles]
You... You
Saiyan trash!
It's about time I
taught you some respect!
[VEGETA grunts]
[DODORIA growling]
[DODORIA chuckles]
[DODORIA]
Heh, heh... Now, Vegeta,
before I start pounding
you to a bloody pulp,
I'm going to give you one
chance to get out of this.
Here's the deal. If you
hand over your scouter
and agree to leave
this planet right now,
I might be
willing to overlook
your foolish
arrogance this time.
I see. So you have lost your
scouters. That's terrible.
How will you and Zarbon
ever find Frieza's backside
to stick your
noses in it?
Ahh!
[VEGETA laughs]
Priceless. No
wonder I was able
to sneak up on
you so easily.
Why, you little--
[VEGETA]
Save it.
[VEGETA chuckles]
[DODORIA growling]
[VEGETA] You can take
your little prize to Frieza.
Far be it for me
to stand in his way.
Here.
It's yours.
I'm surprised,
Vegeta.
I was almost certain I'd
have to pry that scouter
from your
lifeless fingers.
And to tell
you the truth,
I'm more than a
little disappointed
it won't come to that.
But, oh well. We had a deal.
[DODORIA] Ahh!
What are you doing?!
[DODORIA gasps]
Are... you... insane?
Fool! That was the last
scouter on the planet!
It was. And now that it's
gone, I have the advantage.
Ha! What are you
talking about?
You'll be more
lost than I will!
Now you'll never find
Frieza! Or the Nameks!
But you're wrong.
[chuckles]
You see, I've discovered
that it's possible
to sense power levels
without a scouter.
It's one of the many
things I learned
during my
time on Earth.
I could hardly
believe it myself.
But then, I was
forced to rethink
my notions of
impossibility.
[GOKU] Haaa!
Ahh! Nooo!
It was... an enlightening
experience, to say the least.
After that, it was
only a matter of time
before I could duplicate
the technique myself.
Now, I can feel the
energy in the air,
as easily as the
breeze upon my face.
Which means I've
outgrown these silly toys.
I get it...
Those little brats I chased
out here were Earthlings!
They were what?!
[DODORIA] You're
working with them!
You used them to lure
me away from Frieza!
Don't be
such an idiot.
There's no way
those Earth scum
could have gotten
here so quickly.
And even if
there was,
I doubt they'd be in a hurry
to cross my path again.
You are lying!
But guess what?
I killed your little
friends, Vegeta!
And if you stay,
I'll do the same to you!
Final warning.
Go now or feel my wrath!
No, I think I'll stay.
So go ahead. Attack me.
Why, Dodoria,
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were
scared or something.
Let me guess.
You were monitoring
my fight with
Cui earlier.
You've seen
my power!
Zarbon.
What happened?
[ZARBON] I don't know. It must
be some kind of malfunction.
For a second there,
it registered Vegeta's
power level at 22,000.
And then it shorted out.
22,000? You've got
to be kidding me.
It must be that older
model scouter you're using.
[DODORIA gasps]
Well? I'm right,
aren't I?
So you know
you're outmatched.
No! That scouter
was malfunctioning!
You cannot be
that strong!
You can't!
Ahhh...
Haah!
Hah! Hah! Hah! Hah!
[DODORIA growling]
Aahh!
Hah! Are you ready
to believe it now,
or do you still
need more proof?
[DODORIA] Huh? Haah!
[DODORIA grunting]
[DODORIA screaming]
[VEGETA laughing maniacally]
[VEGETA] It's the true
might of a Saiyan warrior!
[DODORIA screaming]
The more we fight, the
stronger our opponents,
the stronger we become.
So, you see, these Earth
fools did me a favor
when they
almost killed me.
I'm more powerful now
than you can imagine.
[DODORIA growling]
[VEGETA laughing]
It's amazing what
a coward you can become
when you're not hiding
behind your master, isn't it?
Too bad Frieza won't
save you this time!
Wait, Vegeta! Please don't
do this to me! I can help you!
I know what really
happened to your homeworld!
[DODORIA yelling]
What's this?
Planet Vegeta was destroyed!
It's gone forever.
What else is
there to know?
If you kill me now,
you're never going to find out!
[DODORIA groaning]
Now, if I tell you,
how do I know you won't
still try to kill me?
You're lucky I don't
kill you where you stand!
So start talking!
Fine, but remember,
I'm only the messenger.
Now, as you know, when
your planet was destroyed,
Frieza told you it had been
struck by a massive meteorite.
Well, that was a lie.
What are you saying?
[DODORIA]
Isn't it obvious?
I'm saying it was
Frieza, not a meteorite
that destroyed
your planet
along with the
entire Saiyan race!
[DODORIA chuckles]
[DODORIA] You see, Frieza
had been using the Saiyans
to do his dirty
work for years.
Compared to many,
they made for
a fairly impressive
breed of warriors.
And since no Saiyan could ever
match Frieza's awesome power,
they were also
relatively easy to control.
Frieza sent teams of Saiyans
to the planets he wanted,
where they would use
their distinctive powers
of transformation to
clear out the opposition.
And for a while, it was a
very productive arrangement.
But over time,
things changed.
While Frieza could still
easily defeat any Saiyan,
several extraordinary fighters,
such as yourself, Vegeta,
were beginning to emerge.
[DODORIA chuckles]
[DODORIA] With
each new victory,
you were becoming more and
more difficult to control.
Your pride was making
you arrogant. Too arrogant.
[VEGETA growling]
[DODORIA] Frieza
could see that it
wouldn't be long
before you tried
to challenge him for
control of the galaxy.
And if left unchecked
he feared that the collective
strength of your race
might actually pose a
serious threat to his power.
And so...
the threat was eliminated.
[DODORIA] With just the
slightest flick of his finger,
your supposedly
mighty civilization
was reduced
to rubble.
[FRIEZA cackling]
But you should be
thankful, Vegeta,
being a prince, and as
talented in battle as you are,
Frieza thought you still
might be useful to us.
[DODORIA] So he sent
you away from the planet
on a special assignment
before he destroyed it.
Personally, I don't know
that I would have made
the same decision.
But then, it wasn't
my decision to make.
[DODORIA] Well, there you
have it. The awful truth.
And now that I've lived up to
my end of our little bargain,
I'll be on my way.
You're not
going anywhere.
Wait a second!
You will pay for
your part in this,
just as Frieza soon will.
But I want you to know
I do this, not for my
planet, not for my race,
but because you
thought you could make
the Prince of Saiyans
a slave to your whim!
[DODORIA] Lord Frieza!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
[DODORIA grunting]
[screaming]
I promise you
this, Frieza...
Your downfall will be at
the hands of a Saiyan!
[GOKU] All right. Time
to get back to work.
I think just one last
session at 20 times gravity
and then I'll be able
to turn it up a notch!
[GOKU] 'Kay! 10,000 push-ups.
[GOKU grunting]
[NARRATOR]
Goku's intensive training
is beginning to bear results,
but in just a
few days time,
his journey will take
him to Planet Namek,
where he must once again face
the ruthless might of Vegeta.
Will our hero be ready
to meet the challenge?
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!