[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan mastered the Z Sword
and it was time to put the
legendary blade to the test.
[GOKU]
Here it comes!
[NARRATOR]
And who better than Goku
to deliver a solid
block of Katchin Ore,
the hardest known
metal in the Universe.
[NARRATOR] But tragedy
struck and the Z Sword
wasn't able to bear
the strain of being handled
by the mighty
father-son duo.
[NARRATOR]
Impossible but true!
The greatest sword ever
made was in pieces.
[NARRATOR] But mystically
emanating from the sword,
after being trapped inside
of it for untold centuries
was Old Kai, an ancient
ancestor of Supreme Kai,
who claimed to have
the ability to awaken
a person's sleeping powers.
Right!
[OLD KAI mumbles nonsensically]
[NARRATOR]
And, with gusto,
he set out to do
just that for Gohan.
But will it really work?
Meanwhile, Trunks and
Goten had finally mastered
the form for the
Fusion Technique
and they were ready to turn
the concept into reality.
[MARON giggles]
[OOLONG]
Stop trying to psyche me out!
[ROSHI]
Just pick!
--[OOLONG grunts]
--[ROSHI chuckles]
[OOLONG]
You're using some of that
mystical master stuff
on me, aren't you?
[BULMA]
She's so cute!
[YAMCHA]
Hey, guys.
[ROSHI]
Hmm?
[VIDEL]
What's up, Yamcha?
Well, it's fusion time.
Trunks and Goten have
mastered the form.
So the boys are ready
to give it a try, huh?
[KRILLIN] Cool!
I say we all go watch.
[BULMA] Yeah, this should
be interesting.
[MARON] Are Trunks
and Goten one boy, Mommy?
[ANDROID 18]
Not yet, sweetheart.
So, ah, if you could
fuse together with somebody
and it could be anyone in
the world, who would it be?
I mean, hypothetically.
Gosh, that's a tough one,
but I think I'd pick your
old girlfriend Maron!
[laughs]
Right on! Bald and
beautiful! So deadly!
Oh, dear!
What are we going to call our
newly combined son, Bulma?
Huh?
Let's see. Goten and Trunks.
What about Trunkten?
Hm. That's weird.
Maybe something like
Gotrunks would be better.
Hey! Why are you
racking your brain?
The fusion's only temporary.
It only lasts about
thirty minutes or so.
True. But still,
a name would be nice.
This oughta be good.
[GOTEN grunts]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[BOTH grunt lightly]
Hey, Trunks.
Hold your power back a bit.
I can try. There.
Yes. That's perfect. Your
levels are exactly the same.
Okay. Whenever you're ready.
[BOTH]
Hm!
This is it.
Hm?
Mm!
Fuuuu...sion!
Haaa!
--[BULMA gasps]
--[CHICHI] Aaah!
Mmhmm!
[KRILLIN exhales quaveringly]
[VIDEL]
This is intense!
[GROUP screams]
[PUAR screams]
Haa... Mmm...
[OX-KING]
ChiChi!
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN]
Mm? Uuh!
[PICCOLO]
Uuh?!
[KRILLIN] Is he supposed
to look like that?
[YAMCHA]
I, uh, guess so.
Wow! He's certainly
well equipped, isn't he?
Yeah! That's a
nice way to put it!
Hey! I think I get it!
He's supposed to
look like that!
He's built like Majin Buu!
[groans]
[KRILLIN] A roly-poly body
must help to regulate
the enormous power
at that level.
That's why Buu has one.
No doubt! Yeah!
Dig it! Check him out!
You've got
the moves, baby! Yeah!
[laughs]
All right!
This is so bizarre!
[groaning]
[YAMCHA] Oh, yeah!
Speed test! Here we go!
[breathing heavily]
Huh?
[panting, wheezing]
[PICCOLO] I think I know
what the problem is.
Huh?
Yeah. We goofed.
Um... Uh...
It's the form. Trunks made
a slight error. He did this.
But he shouldn't have
fully extended his fingers.
He should've done this.
All right! Got it?
Uh...
[PICCOLO] Good!
Now go ahead and separate
so we can get it right.
Well, what are you waiting for?
You heard me. Separate!
Ummm. But, I don't know how.
Huh? Oh, right. I see.
Hmmm.
Uh, well, Goku never
showed us that part.
I guess we don't have a choice.
We'll just have to wait until
the thirty minutes are up.
[KRILIN]
Strange, but you're neither
Trunks or Goten, are you?
[ROSHI] You even have
your own set of clothes.
[VIDEL] What does it
feel like being one person?
Uh. Uh... Uh...
[YAMCHA] Hey, little buddy!
Do you have a name?
Gotenks!
[laughs]
Wow! See, he does
have his own name.
[GOTENKS]
Look. I'm hungry.
I just want to eat
and take a nap.
[MARON] He talks
like Yajirobe, Daddy!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Yeah, he sure does.
Look!
[ROSHI laughs]
--[CHICHI] Goten!
--[BULMA] Thank goodness!
[BOTH gasping]
Did we do it?
I don't know!
Guys! You did it!
You fused! It was great!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Uh. Don't you
remember anything?
No.
Well, congratulations!
You did it!
Yes! Bravo! Well done!
[PICCOLO] Look. We don't have
time for idle talk, you two.
We've got a mission
to accomplish. Got it?
Now let's get back to work!
But, good first try.
[YAMCHA gasps]
Good. Let's go.
[BOTH]
Fuuuu-sion! Ha!
[grunts]
[GROUP gasps]
[CHICHI] Oh, no!
I can't love that!
Why not? He's my age.
No, older.
His ribs are showing!
We need to beef him up
or something!
[PICCOLO grunts]
There'll be no beefing up.
We're going to wait thirty
minutes and try it again.
And this time we're
going to get it right!
[GOTENKS coughs]
This is going
to be a long one.
Boys. Ready?
--[TRUNKS] Mm?
--[GOTEN] Hm!
[BOTH]
Fuuuuu-sion! Haaaa!
[GROUP screams]
Yes! You're doing it!
Stay with it!
[GOTENKS grunts]
Whoa! It worked!
Wow! Feel that? What power!
He's the one all right!
There's no doubt about it!
Wow, he's a cutie!
I think he favors
Trunks a little bit.
Whatd'ya think, ChiChi?
The nose, yes. The eyes, no.
He's got fabulous energy.
Does it matter
who he looks like?
But he does have Goten's hair.
[PICCOLO] Excellent!
Thirty minutes from now
we'll try the fusion again.
Only this time
you'll be Super Saiyans.
Uh, uh, ah! We're not doing
this as Super Saiyans.
What?!
There's no need for it.
We're strong enough as it is.
You little! How dare you!
This is a team effort, got it?
That's a call that
we all have to agree on,
and I don't agree!
It makes no sense to
confront Buu unless you're
at your absolute maximum.
Understand me?
Huh?
Yes. But you don't.
Look. You're scared.
But Buu is nothing.
I will bring him back. Dead!
Uh?
[GOTENKS]
See ya!
Wait! No! Come back!
[GOTENKS]
Don't have a heart attack!
[MR. POPO]
He's not listening!
Oh, good! He's close!
Thirty minutes should be
plenty of time. All right.
This is gonna be fun.
[grunts]
Now that's fast. Whoa.
[PICCOLO] Darn it!
If he gets killed now,
all of our efforts
were for nothing.
Yeah. You're right.
He's reckless for sure.
But I wouldn't be
the least bit surprised
if he beat Majin Buu.
Me either. I betcha that
little guy tears Buu up.
[PICCOLO] If we're lucky.
But what if he doesn't?
[GOKU snoring]
[GOKU] Achoo!
Woo! Aw, man.
[groans]
[yawns]
Welcome back! Nice sleep?
Yeah. It seemed short though.
[SUPREME KAI] Yes. You were
only out for two hours.
Oh! That's right!
How's Gohan?
Are his sleeping
powers awake yet?
[OLD KAI chanting nonsensically]
Eeh!
That's weird.
Yes, Goku. I think
I know what you mean.
And we've still got three hours
to go before the ceremony ends.
Hey. Son. Do your best!
My best! At what?
Being a totem pole!
[OLD KAI]
Ha-aaah!
[BUU] Eeeeh, hee, hee, hee!
Touch down, Buu!
Errrrh! Uh? Huh?
Ohhhhh! Mmhmm!
[laughs]
Buu play with boats!
[chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
Aaah! It's him! Buu!
[PASSENGERS screaming]
[BUU] Da, da, da, da, da!
Da, da, da, daaaaa!
Buu!
--[PASSENGERS screaming]
--[BUU laughing]
Buu make boat
go bye-bye! Bye-bye!
[laughs]
[MAN 2] Somebody help me!
Please! I can't swim!
Buu help?
Help! Please! Help me! Huh?
[grunting]
Thank you! Thank you so much!
[panting]
Aah! M-M-M-M-M-M-Majin...
--[MAN 2 babbles]
--[BUU] Quiet! Mean man!
[MAN 2 yells]
[BUU]
Buu make mean man dead!
[MAN 2 screams]
[BUU giggles]
[grunts]
[GOTENKS]
If you're looking for the guy
who just turned you into
a donut, that would be me.
Hello. You're going to
wish that we never met.
[BUU] Buu no wish!
Buu make boy dead!
[GOTENKS] No, no, no!
Boy make Buu dead! Yes, yes!
[chuckles]
Buu?
Yeah, exactly! See, I'm
way more powerful than you.
You're just a big
overgrown pink doughboy.
Doughboy?
That's right. Ah-heh.
Haa-uh!
[GOTENKS yells]
[chuckles]
[GOTENKS grunts, yells]
[laughs]
[yells]
[GOTENKS]
That fat tub is fish flakes
after a blast
like that. Bummer!
I told Piccolo I'd
bring Buu back dead.
Then I go and
blow him to pieces.
Great. How am I
gonna handle this one?
[splash]
[GOTENKS] What in the world?
Buu's butt! And his legs!
Woo!
[laughs]
Mean boy call Buu fat!
Buu blow steam!
Look, you're fat.
There's no getting around it.
[grunts]
Buu make you dead!
Aaah!
Missed--uh!
[GOTENKS thinking]
Man, that was fast.
He read me like a book.
[GOTENKS]
Hey! Nice move, tubby!
He-heh.
[BUU grunts]
[GOTENKS] Aah!
[BUU]
Buu hit mean boy!
[laughs]
[GOTENKS groans]
[GOTENKS] Aaah!
[groans]
[BUU laughs]
Now boy die!
[laughs]
[blasts]
Huh?
[COMMANDER] Majin Buu,
you are under arrest.
Surrender immediately
or we will open fire!
All right, men! Fire!
Hey! Are you crazy?
Get the heck out of here!
You can't beat him!
[PILOT] Captain! Target is
engulfed in flames!
[COMMANDER] That's it men!
Keep it coming!
[COMMANDER] Wait! Cease fire!
Target's on the move!
What? He's fine!
Uuh! Mean men! Mean!
No! Run! He's going to attack!
[bellows]
[PILOT yells]
Men! Retreat!
[yells]
Woohoo! Buu go bang, bang!
Wow! He's alive!
[CHICHI]
Did you do it, Gotenks?
[BULMA]
Did you beat Majin Buu?
[GOTENKS]
Not exactly.
He's a, heh, a little
tougher than I thought.
[ALL] Uuuh!
[PICCOLO]
So, you're back.
Serves you right!
You fool! You could've blown
our only chance to win!
From now on
we do things my way!
Tomorrow you're going to
fight Buu as a Super Saiyan
and until then, we train!
Understood? Trunkten?
[MR. POPO]
Actually it's Gotenks.
What?!
[MR. POPO] His name.
It's uh, Gotenks.
[PICCOLO] His name is Mud
as far as I'm concerned.
[OLD KAI chants nonsensically]
[NARRATOR] The Old Kai is
a movin' and a groovin',
but will his efforts pay off?
Can the wizened sage really
awaken Gohan's latent powers?
The question really is,
can Gohan wait another
thirty hours to find out?
And after being beaten
roundly by Majin Buu,
can Gotenks
rebound and conquer
as a fused Super Saiyan?