[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
a strong new
version of Majin Buu,
now dominated by hatred,
arrived atop the Lookout,
and when Piccolo could not
produce the challenger,
who had been promised,
Majin Buu unleashed
a horrific power:
The Human Extinction Attack.
[NARRATOR] Out of the entire
population of Earth,
less than twenty
humans now remain.
It was a blow
that would lay heavily
on Piccolo's conscience.
Human Extinction Attack!
How do you like it?
Now where is the strong one?
I see. Yes. We just need
a short time to prepare him.
He... He can be ready
in one hour if that's okay?
Please, Buu!
What's an hour?
How long is it?
[NARRATOR] Realizing Goten and
Trunks were not strong enough
to fight this altered form,
Piccolo has managed
to buy one hour's time,
time that will be
stretched to its maximum
as the two young fighters enter
the Hyperbolic Time Chamber
for final, desperate training.
Will Piccolo's
daring plan succeed?
Man, is that really Majin Buu?
If it is, he must
be on a big diet.
[PICCOLO]
Make no mistake.
That is Majin Buu
and his strength has
increased substantially.
You boys need to understand.
We're in a very grave
situation, things have changed.
For every minute out here
you can train six hours
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber.
Maybe that's enough.
Mom, where are you going?
What?!
Whatever it is you're
doing ChiChi, stop it.
You savage, do you even care
that you killed my oldest son?!
You look at me when
I'm talking to you!
[gasping]
Do you like eggs?
Huh?
[screams]
Ahhhhh!
My mother...
[GOTEN] I'll get you,
you stupid beast!
[PICCOLO]
No, Goten!
You go down and we're all dead!
But Mom was all I had left.
Goten...
Listen we can bring your mother
back with the Dragon Balls
provided only one thing,
that you and Trunks stay alive
long enough to
wipe out Majin Buu!
[PICCOLO] There is no way
to beat him at your current
power levels, and we've
got less than an hour left
so the two of you
must train quickly.
Can you do it?
[GOTEN]
Uh-huh.
Yeah, sure you can Goten!
We've all lost someone by now-
but that just means we have
to beat Buu harder! Right?!
[GOTEN]
Mm-hmm.
That's right!
Wow, this place is cool.
I wonder if they've
got any food around here?
My body feels kinda
weird and heavy.
Hey Goten, do you feel that?
Hey, you don't have to be
in such a rush you know!
A minute on the other side is
like hours and hours over here,
so we've got time to spare.
Huh?!
Piccolo forgot to mention
there's nothing to eat.
Wow, Goten,
whoever was in here last
must've really wiped it out!
Nothing but brown rice
and water in the fridge!
I don't know about you
but I could really
go for a roast beef
sandwich or...
Huh?!
Hey, don't start without me!
[TRUNKS]
Wait a second.
[VIDEL]
Piccolo?
Hmm?
[VIDEL] Earlier when you
were speaking to Majin Buu,
you talked about my father like
the two of them knew each other.
[PICOOLO]
Yes.
[VIDEL]
But I don't get it.
How could my father
have known Majin Buu?
Your father is a hero,
he took it upon himself to
journey to Majin Buu's home
and fight him on his own ground.
[PICCOLO]
For reasons we don't know,
Mr. Satan did
not fight Majin Buu.
Instead, the two
forged a friendship.
Your father is
the only human being
Majin Buu seems to appreciate.
Although other circumstances
brought it to a halt,
your father nearly made
Buu adopt a life of peace.
He may have transformed
into this evil entity now,
but Buu still has a
potent memory of a man
and the kindness
he showed a monster.
Your dad will never have
the powers that we do, Videl.
But his compassion
exceeds any victory
he could ever
achieve in the ring.
My dad...?
[SUPER BUU growls]
Aaaaaaaaahh!
No more, no more waiting!
No, it's only been
thirty minutes!
Wait! You won't have a
challenge if you fight him now!
The hour isn't over!
I'm done. I'm done waiting.
I'm fighting.
Come out!! Do you hear me?!
Aaaaahhh!
[KRILLIN]
Watch out!
Hurry up!
Ow!
That's gonna
hurt in the morning...
[YAMCHA]
Whoa, this isn't good.
Why don't we get
Trunks and Goten?
They've got to have finished
their training by now!
Would you stop
worrying about yourself?!
[KRILLIN] Oh, forget the
morning, it hurts right now.
What happened out here?
Okay, I'll take you
to him. Let's go.
[PICCOLO]
It's this way.
It looks like Piccolo
is taking him right
to the Hyperbolic Time Chamber.
Goten and Trunks
won't be expecting Buu
to pop his head in that early!
[YAMCHA]
That's weird.
Why doesn't Piccolo just
bring out Goten and Trunks?
[KRILLIN] You think they're
actually going to fight inside?
If they do fight
Majin Buu inside
the Hyperbolic Time Chamber
and the entrance is destroyed,
then that dimension will
be closed off from this one.
Even if Trunks and Goten lose,
Earth might still be saved.
But whoever is left inside
will be trapped, maybe forever.
Ahh!
Hey!
But we can't wish them back
from another dimension, can we?
[PICCOLO] The Dragon Balls
are not bound by the limits
of different dimensions.
We will be able to wish
them back, if they're killed.
Well, it sure seems like Piccolo
has cooked up one mean strategy.
[ROSHI] Oh! Speaking of
what's cookin'... Hehehehe!
[BULMA growls]
[SUPER BUU] Do we have to
climb all of these stairs?
[PICCOLO]
I'm afraid so.
[KRILLIN] Well, at least
they're walking slow.
Roshi!
You're facing the wrong way!
Oh! Hahaha! Thanks for the
directional help, honey.
Doesn't it seem like Piccolo's
taking the long way around?
Yes. He's missed three turns
that would have taken
him directly to the room.
[KRILLIN] I bet he's stalling
to give them more time.
I mean since one minute
over here is worth six hours
in the time chamber, the
longer he takes, the better.
Come on, how far is it?
Not too far, we have to go down
a few flights to reach them.
[SUPER BUU] Down? After
climbing up all this way?
[PICCOLO] I assure you,
it's the only way to get there.
[GOTENKS]
Gotenks, over and out.
Man, that's a work out.
Hahaha.
It sure is neat to know
there's levels even higher
than Super Saiyan, huh?
Hmph! Now there's no
way he can beat us.
We weren't half this
strong when we came in here.
Trunks, I'm beat.
It feels like all of my energy
has just fallen
right out of my body.
And I think we might still
have a problem with time.
[TRUNKS]
Let's look.
[TRUNKS] See, by the time
we figured out our trick,
we only had five minutes
left before we separated.
Okay, so we'll try jumping
to the new super level
as soon as we fuse,
and then we'll beat
him in like four minutes!
But that's stupid
to win so fast!
Warriors drag out their
fights as long as possible!
I'm telling you, Goten, after
this week of training in here,
we're strong enough
to fight off Buu
even if we don't turn
into a regular Super Saiyan!
So, I'm thinking we
start fighting him
with our normal fusion,
getting in as many
hits as we can, right?
Spending as much time
as possible playing around.
Then we make it look like
we can't take anymore,
and that's when
we spring it on him!
We go to our new
Super Saiyan thing
as fast as we
can and we got him!
By that time he'll
tired and confused!
It'll be the kind of move
people will never forget!
Uh-huh. Hahaha!
Then he'll be sorry for
what he did to Gohan,
and your mom, and my dad! Ha!
Yeah, that's the plan.
Where are they?!
[PICCOLO thinking] Please,
don't run out of patience yet.
It's not far now.
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Goten, Trunks, can you hear me?
--Huh?
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Don't be frightened, boys.
It's me, Piccolo.
Piccolo?
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Be quiet and listen
very carefully to me.
The two of you are
going to fight Majin Buu
earlier than expected.
He's on his way
to you as I speak.
Ahhh! But we're so tired,
I don't know if we have the
energy to stand up right now.
[PICCOLO telepathically]
It's all right, Goten.
I'm taking the long way around
to give you some extra time.
We should arrive at
the door in one minute.
That gives you six
hours to recuperate.
Do everything you
can to prepare. Sleep.
Drink some water.
Stretch your muscles out.
I believe in you boys.
We all do.
And I'm counting
on you to finish this.
[PICCOLO telepathically]
Good luck to you both.
Hah!
Six hours is more
than enough time for us.
You know what Trunks?
For the first time ever,
I actually feel
sorry for Majin Buu.
[laughing]
Would you care to
eat before the fight?
No!
I don't want to eat.
You take me there now,
before I break you in half!
[PICCOLO]
Of course.
Here we are.
Where is he?
[SUPER BUU]
Hmm?
You ready, Goten?
Yeah!
What about Buu?
Doesn't look it.
Cool, let's do this.
Those kids?
[PICCOLO]
That's right.
[PICCOLO thinking] Even if these
boys are perfectly trained,
we still need a miracle.
All that training
and Piccolo is the only
one who came to watch us.
Why didn't anyone else come?
Where is the fighter?
It's them.
[TRUNKS] We might
not have an audience,
but let's still
give a good show.
[GOTEN]
Mm-hmm.
This is the end for you...
...Majin Buu.
Don't you think
it's a little bit stupid
that I just say "Majin Buu."
You had a few more lines there.
Is it my fault if
you can't remember them?
Let's begin!
[TRUNKS] Looks like the
bad guy's getting impatient.
Should we show him our moves?
Oh, all right.
Ready?
Let's go!
[TRUNKS]
Ow!! What's wrong with you?
You can't just come in swinging
like that, without any warning.
Don't you know
what a sucker punch is?
That's something only
inexperienced fighters do.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
We're trying to prepare so
we can give you a fair fight.
So why don't YOU
try some, patience?
Now, we're going to power up.
You stand there and be quiet.
I'll tell you when
it's time to fight.
Let's try this
thing again. Ready?
Yep!
[BOTH]
Go!
Fu--
[PICOLO thinking]
What are they doing?
Why aren't they starting
as Super Saiyans?
[BOTH]
--sion!
Ha!
That's perfect! Their power
levels are exactly equal.
Ha!
Nice to see you
again Majin Buu!
Ah, yes. There's my fighter,
too bad no one else is here
to witness your final hour.
Final hour?
That's pretty clever.
Guess you can tell jokes now
that you're not a tub of lard!
But I've been changing too and
you're in for a real surprise
when my fists start flying.
This is really stunning.
His power level has
increased dramatically.
Maybe he can actually win this.
Huh? Huh?
You said you'd tell me
when I can start fighting.
Yeah, okay just wait
here for a second.
[GOTENKS thinking]
So much for the plan.
After that kind of attack,
he's not even bruised.
I'll just have to show
him a few of my secrets.
[NARRATOR]
It looks like Majin Buu
is even stronger than
the boys had predicted.
But Gotenks has several
more tricks up his sleeve.
The only question is:
Will they be enough?
This could be a problem.