[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell was in the final
stages of his evolution
to become the Ultimate Android!
It looked like all our
heroes could do was stand back
and watch in terror as he
morphed into the most powerful
machine in the universe!
With haunting visions of
the future plaguing his mind,
Trunks tried desperately
to stop the transformation!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[grunting continues]
[CELL roars]
[TRUNKS yells]
[NARRATOR] But it was too late.
[NARRATOR] Nothing could
stop Cell from changing.
[NARRATOR] And so, with
one Earth-shaking blast,
it finally happened.
[NARRATOR] Cell was complete.
Vegeta... it's your fault!
[NARRATOR] While the
other fighters trembled,
Vegeta could only smile
at this latest development.
After all, he's the
one who let it happen.
[VEGETA] I don't have
anything to worry about!
[NARRATOR} But seeing
the horrible monster who
had absorbed Android
18 was too much for Krillin.
And against all odds,
the heartbroken hero
lashed out at Cell
with blow after angry blow.
Chew on this!
Destructo Disc!
[NARRATOR} But as much as
Krillin wanted Cell to go down,
the mighty android
proved to be invincible
to Krillin's every attempt.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Krillin get out of there!
[NARRATOR] And with
one dynamic kick,
it appears that Cell
has added Krillin
to the long list of lives
he has destroyed.
[NARRATOR] Can anyone stop
this heartless villain?
Find out today!
No! Krillin, no!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[coughing]
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL chuckles]
D-Did someone get
the number of that bus?
I... I've never felt anything
so painful in my life...
It's as if all my bones
are totally crushed!
[KRILLIN] But don't worry about
me, no sir. I'll be just fine.
[KRILLIN chuckles weakly]
I hope I'm not rude, but
I'm gonna take a little nap...
Just hold on!
[CELL chuckles softly]
Hah! He should feel lucky.
He's the first one to be
touched by my perfect body.
[TRUNKS] Krillin! No!
You've got to hang in there!
I won't let it end like this!
I need you to try
to swallow this!
Everything will be alright.
It's a Senzu bean.
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] Don't tell
me you're satisfied
swatting flies like him.
Guess a guy like you needs
any victory he can get.
[VEGETA] From the way
you've been carrying on,
I was expecting a
true challenge.
If that's your idea of perfect,
I might as well go home.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I was hoping you'd stay.
Destroying you would
be a decent warm-up.
Alright. But this time,
don't whine when I beat you.
I won't.
[CELL chuckles]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[TRUNKS sighs]
[TRUNKS] There you go, easy now.
[KRILLIN groans]
[TRUNKS] Welcome back, Krillin!
I almost thought you were
too far gone to make it!
What's the matter?
Oh no! Vegeta's
about to bite it!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[KRILLIN] I might not be as
strong as a Super Saiyan...
But there's one thing
I know first hand...
And that is, how incredibly
powerful Cell has become!
Trust me!
He's a lot stronger
than he's letting on!
I felt it, Trunks.
It was only for a second,
but when he kicked me
I could sense his true power!
[CELL chuckles]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA laughs]
Cell's power
went up dramatically...
But by my calculations, Vegeta
still holds the advantage.
[KRILLIN] No, you can't let
the energy you detect
from Cell fool you.
It's all just a front.
His real power is
a whole lot bigger.
He's hiding it, like you.
You mean you know?
[VEGETA yells]
[grunting]
Well, it's nice to see
you've become a little stronger.
Maybe this time I'll
actually break a sweat!
Knowing Vegeta,
he's probably too caught up
in himself to notice.
But yeah, I can sense
that you're holding back.
You've got a lot more power in
you than you're making public
don't you?
Well, if you have
all that strength,
why haven't you
stopped Cell yet?!
Tell me!
[VEGETA growls]
Come on! You're going to have to
try harder if you want to live.
[CELL chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA thinking]
He's gotten so fast!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL yells]
[VEGETA growls]
My father, has gone beyond
the powers of a Super Saiyan.
[CELL chuckles]
So, I see you were
holding out on me after all.
Of course, compared to me,
you're still an inferior cretin.
You were a fool to
spend all that time
absorbing the androids.
If you really wanted power, you
should've gone after a Saiyan!
Hah! Like you, right?
Yes, but of course.
[CELL chuckles]
[TRUNKS] Near the
end of our training,
my father reached a
plateau and I surpassed him.
But I can't let my father know,
because he'll hate me for it!
I've worked so hard
to gain his approval,
and I'm still not there yet.
I know he'll accept me
once he sees how strong I am.
But not now. I have to
wait until he's ready.
[KRILLIN] But, Trunks...
He should have
beaten Cell back there
when he still had the chance!
Vegeta's strength
is hard to believe.
He'd dead even with
Cell in his final stage.
[PICCOLO] It won't last.
Huh...?
He isn't thinking. Vegeta
has let his anger take control
and it's making his
fighting technique sloppy.
That's no way to fight.
Would you two stop whispering
to each other for once,
and tell me what's
going on down there?!
This isn't a boys
only club, you know!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOKU] That's it, Gohan!
Keep going!
Okay, okay! Now
you're really starting
to get control of your
energy! That's good!
[yelling, grunting]
[GOKU] Now, try
to push it forward!
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU] Excellent!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOKU] You're actually
starting to scare me!
[BOTH grunting]
[CELL chuckles]
[VEGETA] Hmm...
Huh?!
You coward...
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA shouts]
[shouting continues]
Here I come!
[VEGETA gasps]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] You impress me, Vegeta.
That was quite a little show.
[VEGETA growls]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Hmm...
[VEGETA] How dare you
play me for a fool?!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yelling]
[yelling continues]
What happened?
I-I get the feeling that
Vegeta's starting to lose it!
I never guessed 18 would
give Cell this much power.
Now we are all doomed.
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
How could Dr. Gero
have created such a monster?
[VEGETA] Huh--?!
[VEGETA growls]
I'll squash you!
[VEGETA snarls]
[VEGETA growls]
Father...
Are there any limits
to his power?
That's all I can stand!
You're not taking
this seriously!
But I told you, Vegeta,
I'm just warming up.
Huh?
Cell's gotten to him!
He's blinded by anger!
[CELL chuckles]
"Just warming up"?!
I think you're too
afraid to fight me, Cell!
Oh, sure, you might have a
brand new body, but inside,
you haven't changed
one little bit!
You're still the
same as you were...
a sniveling, spineless coward!
If you're as powerful
as you say you are,
then let's see what
you're made of!
With pleasure.
I will not tolerate
this childish little game!
Yeah! He got 'em!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA gasps]
No...
[CELL chuckles]
"Super Vegeta!"
[KRILLIN] Did you see that?
Vegeta gave him
a boot to the head
and it didn't even phase him!
I told you! Cell's
turned into some kinda...
some kinda mechanical freak!
Trunks you've gotta
unleash your power!
It's the only way to beat him!
I can't! With my father's
pride as strong as it is
he would never let anyone
interfere, especially not me!
He'd rather lose than
accept someone's help.
That's ridiculous!
[CELL chuckles]
That's it. Vegeta's finished.
[NARRATOR] As Cell closes in,
could this really be
the end of Vegeta?
Or will Trunks go against
his father's wishes
to save his life?
The monster
continues his warpath,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!