[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku had mounted
what looked like
a final assault against Frieza.
[GOKU] Mark my words,
I'm going to win this fight!
So get ready, Frieza,
'cause this time,
you're going down!
[NARRATOR] Firing up his
Twenty Times Kaio-Ken,
Goku turned into a
Saiyan cannon ball,
aimed directly at Frieza!
[NARRATOR] A quick
jab with the left...
A mean hook
with the right...
[GOKU] Kamehame-Haa!
[NARRATOR] And Goku threw
Frieza against the ropes
with his powerful Kamehameha.
[NARRATOR] Frieza tried his
hardest to stop the blast,
but not even he could keep
this bomb from going off.
[NARRATOR] At last,
the evil lizard
had a taste of his own medicine.
[NARRATOR] For a moment,
it looked as if Goku
had actually destroyed
Frieza, once and for all.
[NARRATOR] The universe
was safe again.
[NARRATOR] But when
the smoke cleared,
Frieza was still standing,
virtually untouched!
[NARRATOR] Another round between
Goku and Frieza begins... today!
[KRILLIN] Oh no...
The Twenty Times
Kaio-Ken didn't work!
[GOKU] This can't be!
I-I didn't even scratch him!
I... guess that means Frieza
wasn't lying about his power...
Which means he is
the strongest fighter
in the universe and
I don't stand a chance.
[BULMA groans]
Wh-Where in the
world am I...?
Ah...
'Kay... Let me think...
There was that frog...
Or was I a frog?
Uhhh...
I remember seeing
Krillin and Gohan...
[BULMA screams]
This is all crazy!
I just can't sit
here and wait!
I've got to take the
bull by the horns
and go fight that
stupid alien.
And if something
happens to me...
[GINYU grunting]
[GINYU sighs]
I gotcha!
You're the slime-ball
who got me into this mess!
[GINYU whimpers]
What's goin' on here?
Goku's Kamehameha attack was
awesome, but nothing happened!
Yeah...
[KRILLIN] How is it possible
that it had no
effect on Frieza?
[GOHAN] I guess my Dad
is losing his power again...
[KRILLIN] Well, then I guess
it's true. Frieza is invincible!
[PICCOLO] The fight
is over for Goku.
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN] Huh?
King Kai was
right all along.
Before this even started,
he warned us to avoid
Frieza at all cost.
[thinking] Something is
strange about this warrior.
How does a Saiyan have
such incredible power?
They are after all
inferior creatures...
I've never met a fighter
with that kind of strength.
[FRIEZA growls]
[thinking] I must
take him out now!
[FRIEZA growls]
Prepare for battle!
It is time...
...for your demise.
[FRIEZA growls]
It's all over, Saiyan!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU screams]
I'm coming, Dad!
[GOHAN growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
You weakling.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU coughs]
Well, the
choice is yours.
Are you ready to surrender?
[FRIEZA snarls]
[YAMCHA] King Kai!
What's going on down there?!
[KING KAI] It seems that our
friend has been defeated.
That's just not possible!
Th-There is nothing
we can do now.
As I suspected,
there is no being alive that can
bring down the almighty Frieza!
[GOKU grunts]
Well, my friend...
I hope that slapped a
little sense into you.
[FRIEZA] I guess I was mistaken
when I thought you'd be the one
smart enough to join me.
Oh well, just one less
Saiyan to worry about.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[thinking] My energy is
starting to fade fast...
And I don't know if I have
anything left to attack with.
This doesn't look good...
I realize all you Saiyans
want to do is fight,
but fighting is useless.
Unless, of course, you
are superior like me.
And that is why I took the
liberty of wiping out your kind.
[VEGETA] Kakarot! Listen to me!
Is that all the power you have?
Where's your Saiyan pride?!
But... But I never
was a Saiyan...
[VEGETA] Nonsense! What
are you talking about?!
You can't deny your heritage!
Vegeta...
Right now it doesn't
matter what I am...
Forget about it!
[GOKU gasps]
You must listen to me.
We both that know you
have Saiyan blood
running through your veins.
I feel your pain.
But you must never
forget one thing:
It was Frieza who destroyed our
birthplace, the Planet Vegeta.
And now that you are
the only Saiyan left,
it is up to you to
avenge our race!
Th-The pride... of my people.
Think back, Kakarot!
Remember your
father... My father...
There's no one
left except for you.
[BARDOCK] My...
son... lives on...
[KING VEGETA groans]
So while you may
deny who you are...
[VEGETA] You are
the very last hope
for a lost race of
brave warriors!
Ask yourself this:
Why does Frieza want
you destroyed so badly?
He's afraid a
Super Saiyan will rise up.
The strongest of all!
Destroy him...
Destroy him for the
entire Saiyan race.
Destroy him, for you have
the power within you!
[VEGETA] Now go,
Kakarot, it is time.
Do all that is within your
power to bring down Frieza!
[FRIEZA] Excuse me, I hate
to interrupt your daydream,
but I've got a job to finish.
Good Riddance,
you sniffling...
SAIYAN!
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA] I had you
scared, didn't I?
So now, I say we
have a little fun.
Vegeta...
I grew up on planet Earth,
I don't know how to be a Saiyan!
But...
I share in your
disgust for Frieza!
Is your brave,
little speech over?
I must win!
I will not let you beat me!
No! You lose!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[GOKU] Haah!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[FRIEZA] What the--?!
[grunting continues]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA] I see you've got
some of your energy back.
Or was that all you had left?
[GOKU groans]
[FRIEZA] My guess is that
you're all out of gas.
[FRIEZA] You see, I can read
you like a book, my friend.
And it's time to finish the
last chapter with a bang...
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU grunting]
You can do it, Dad...
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA] Let's see you
get out of this one.
[FRIEZA] I must say
I'm impressed.
Said the spider
to the fly.
[KING KAI growls]
[BUBBLES chatters]
[KING KAI] Huh?!
Listen! What's going on?
It sounds
like Bubbles.
And it's coming from
inside the house.
[BUBBLES chattering excitedly]
[BUBBLES groaning]
[GREGORY groans]
[YAMCHA] What
happened, Bubbles?!
[CHIAOTZU] Gregory...
[BUBBLES chatters excitedly]
[TIEN] It looks like
there's somebody in there...
[multiple voice mumbling]
Hey, you!
Who are you guys?!
Recoome!
Burter!
I'm Jeice!
Guldo!
All of us together are...
the one and only Ginyu Force!
[JIECE] That wasn't very good!
[ALL muttering]
All of us together are...
the one and only Ginyu Force!
[GULDO] We stink
without our leader.
[BURTER] Not to mention
we're out of practice!
[RECOOME] Let's give
'em some Ginyu Spirit!
[BURTER] Yeah!
That's what we need!
Ginyu Spirit!
[JEICE] Then let's do it again!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Who... are they...?
They're whacko.
[GOHAN growls]
I've had enough of this!
I'm going to help him!
No, wait!
I can't!
My dad's getting
destroyed out there!
Be patient!
Goku isn't finished yet!
[PICCOLO] If my guess is right,
Frieza is in for a big surprise.
[FRIEZA] What?
What is he doing?
That's the
Spirit Bomb!
What? "Spirit Bomb"?
The ultimate attack...
Goku was personally trained by
the master himself, King Kai.
It actually draws
energy from the planet
and everything on it.
From mountains and
trees, animals, people...
Right down to the smallest
micro-organisms.
[KRILLIN] And when the
force is strong enough,
it's released in one
massive ball of energy.
Really...?
Maybe Freiza won't have
the last laugh after all.
But, will the energy
ball be strong enough
to take out Frieza?
Because there are hardly any
living things on this planet
to draw energy from!
I can see that!
But we have to trust in
Goku's instincts, Gohan!
It's our only defense
against that monster Frieza!
It's all we have left...
[thinking] This planet
doesn't have near the energy
I need to defeat him.
But if I concentrate, maybe
there's a chance I can draw
what I need from the
stars of Planet Namek.
[thinking] I know I shouldn't
use the Spirit Bomb Attack...
its force could wipe
out this entire planet.
[thinking] But if I
don't, Frieza could
destroy the Universe, so I
really don't have a choice!
[thinking] Get
ready, Frieza!
It's time to take out
the heavy artillery!
[FRIEZA]
Oh, look. How cute...
The little Saiyan is
trying to scare me
with pathetic water tricks.
[FRIEZA] Pity...
He tries so hard.
C'mon...
You just gotta come
through for us!
Give it your best shot!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[PICCOLO gasps]
Wh-What was that?!
C'mon, tell me!
I... don't know...
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN] Hey! Look!
Look at that!
There, up in the sky!
Huh?!
[KRILLIN gasps]
That's...
That's the Spirit Bomb!
And it's about
to detonate!
[NARRATOR] Is Goku truly strong
enough to stop Frieza,
the ultimate fighting machine?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!