[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Captain Ginyu had used his
amazing "Metamorphosing" power
to switch bodies with Goku.
Meanwhile, Krillin and Gohan
uncovered all seven Dragon Balls
And with Vegeta lurking
in the shadows,
they began to call
the Namekian Dragon!
I command you now!
Hear my howl, to make
my wish come true!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[GOHAN laughs]
[NARRATOR] But their hopes
were dashed as they realized
they didn't possess
the necessary password.
[NARRATOR] To make
matters worse,
Jeice and the disguised Captain
Ginyu arrived at the scene.
[GINYU shouts]
[NARRATOR] And when
Captain Ginyu realized
Gohan and Krillin
weren't fooled,
he attempted to
take them out!
Will Goku's arrival
make a difference?
Find out today!
[GINYU shouting]
[BOTH whimpering]
[JEICE] Huh...?
[VEGETA gasps]
[GINYU shouting]
[GOKU grunts]
[shouting continues]
[GINYU laughs]
Jeice!
Check out your scouter display
and give me a strength reading!
Right!
[GINYU shouts]
Huh...? Ah...
Now, Jeice!
Hurry up, would ya?!
Uh... You're at 23,000?
Jeice! Would you
please speak up!
Ah... Uhhh...
23,000 Captain!
Huh?
Uhh...
Yeah! Now...
you two... are toast!
Uhh...
You pint sized
pukes don't stand a
chance against ME!
Huh?! 23?!
And... getting weaker...
Huh?
Uhh...
[GINYU] It's not possible!
Maybe you should
check it again, Jeice...
[GOKU] You still don't
get it, do you Ginyu?!
Unless you know how
to use your mind
and your body
as one, together,
you'll only get
weaker and weaker!
Krillin! Gohan! Now's the
time to take him out!
[GINYU whimpers]
Hrrrgh...
Yaah!
You little...!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[KRILLIN] Maybe Goku's right!
Maybe we can beat that
Ginyu geek after all!
Now, Gohan!
Yeah, right!
[GINYU growls]
Get 'em, Gohan!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
What're you
waiting for?!
But... it's Daddy!
Raagh!
Gohan!
What's wrong, Gohan?!
I... just can't...
hit him, Krillin, because he
looks exactly like my father!
[GINYU growls]
I know what you mean,
it is hard to fight this guy
when he inside your dad's body.
But get it through your head,
Gohan, this is not your father!
Understand?
[GOHAN growls]
[GOKU growls]
'Kay. I think I'm ready.
Haah!
[GINYU shouts]
[GOHAN yells]
[blows landing]
Hrraagh!
[blows landing,
yelling]
[grunting]
[GINYU growls]
[BOTH grunt]
[GINYU] Jeice!
Huh?!
Don't just
stand there!
Maybe you could help
me a little bit here?!
Right! Coming!
[VEGETA] Hey, Snow White!
How 'bout you pick on
somebody your own size?
[VEGETA chuckles]
[thinking] Vegeta...
It-It-It's Vegeta. But
what would he be doing here?
[KRILLIN shouts]
Huh?!
[blows landing]
[GINYU growls]
Raah!
Yaah!
Hey, Captain Ginyu!
You can't fool me anymore!
What...
What's going on?!
I should have plenty of
strength in this body,
I-I just don't understand!
[KRILLIN] You really
don't get it, do you?
Didn't you hear
what Goku said?
You gotta use your
mind and your body!
Now that
you understand,
how about surrendering?
Sur... Surrender?
A captain in the Ginyu
Force surrender?!
Surrender THIS!
Yaah!
[blows landing,
yelling]
[GINYU] Eat knuckles!
[JEICE] Pretty stupid to
challenge me to a fight,
huh, tough guy?!
Look who's
chasing who, pal!
[blows landing]
So, Vegetable Breath,
where exactly were you hiding?
My scouter didn't
show you anywhere!
Well, I guess it goes to
show you how behind the times
your useless Ginyu
technology is!
[blows landing,
grunting]
Time to finish you off, punk!
I hope you realize
that up till now
I've only been
toying with you!
In your dreams, Vegeta!
That'll be the day a
wimpy Saiyan like you
can beat even the weakest
of the Ginyu Force!
And now, it's time to turn
out your lights, you loser!
[JEICE grunts]
[VEGETA laughs]
Huh?
[laughing continues]
[VEGETA] I hate to admit this,
but I must say I'm impressed!
You're a lot tougher
than I thought!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Take a look at
your scouter
and then you'll realize
what you're up against!
[JEICE] I am! And
that's what's so funny!
But just to humor you,
I'll check it again and see
if I even get a reading!
It's... impossible!
Nooo!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] I think you broke it!
No kidding!
[VEGETA] You see, unlike the
Saiyan you've been fighting,
I get excited at the
prospect of finishing off
a warrior who's
weaker than I.
And you're much weaker.
So do you feel like
taking on a real Saiyan?
Well, do you punk?
Because if you do, come
and get a piece of me!
[VEGETA] Come on.
I haven't got all day!
I'm waiting.
Let's get this over with.
[JEICE gasps]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Wha--? No way!
Are you telling me
you're a Super Saiyan?
[VEGETA laughs]
That's right, amigo,
I'm your worst nightmare,
live and in person
and ready to rumble!
So, if you think
you stand a chance
against a Super Saiyan,
be my guest!
I... will... defeat you!
[JEICE yells]
[JEICE gasps]
[grunts]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[GINYU growls]
It's just like
Goku said,
this guy isn't so
tough after all!
Right!
I think we can take
him down, Krillin!
I hope you're both
wearing clean underwear
because you two are
about to take a trip
to the emergency ward!
Go, Goku!
Heed my warning before
it's too late!
You must leave the planet now!
Goku... If only I could help
you in some other way I would,
but, for now, please listen!
The Dark Force nears!
And if you and the others
don't leave, you will face
the omnipotent wrath of Frieza!
[NAIL growls]
[grunting]
[NAIL yells]
Got... to stall him...
Got to hold on to give
the Earthlings more time!
[NAIL groans]
Well, I must
say, you Nameks
are really quite a
stubborn breed...
But I see your energy
is running low...
So, to be sporting, I'll make
this as painless as possible!
Dende!
[GURU] Everyday I
wonder how much time
I have left to
watch over Namek...
Now my only hope is that
Dende will arrive in time
to save the people from Earth.
[GURU] It is up
to you now, Dende.
Oh... If Guru
doesn't survive,
then the Dragon Balls
will all disappear.
I must hurry.
I just couldn't
live with myself if
something happened.
[distant grunting]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[fighting sounds continue]
Keep it up, guys!
[fighting sounds]
[blows landing]
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN] Gohan!
[GINYU chuckles]
I don't know what's
going on around here!
Isn't he supposed to be
losing his strength?
I'd say we'd better
watch it, Gohan!
Yeah! Right!
[GOKU grunts]
It looks like he's
figured out my powers!
[GOKU grunts]
Be careful, Gohan!
[GINYU chuckles]
Bingo! Give the
man a silver dollar
because Captain Ginyu's
back in action!
Get ready! The Captain's
comin' to get youuu!
Ah man, that attack line
really sucked the big one.
I gotta come up with
something better...
Now what would a Captain
of the Ginyu Force
say that sounds really tough?
[KRILLIN yells]
[blows landing]
Hey... wait, cueball!
I wasn't ready yet!
[blows landing]
Raah!
All right, then! I'm
not taking this anymore!
Haah!
That was only the
appetizer, kiddo!
[GINYU] Hyaah!
[GOHAN gasps]
Gohan! Look out!
[GOHAN screams]
[GOKU shouts]
Gohan!
Da-Daddy...?
Both of you should
have been annilated!
Sorry... to
dissappoint you...
but I've learned how
your body works too!
And now you'll have
to contend with me!
[GINYU growls]
Now... Let's see what
you can do when it's
three fighters that you're
trying to bully around!
We better stop
that guy now
before he figures out
my body's full power!
Game over, Ginyu!
Krillin! Gohan!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
[ALL grunt]
Never thought
I'd be doing this.
Uh... You think we
can beat him, Daddy?
Yes... I'm
sure of it, son.
But it's definitely
going to feel strange
fighting against
my own body!
[JEICE yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[JEICE] If you thought
you'd seen the last of me,
think again!
[JEICE shouts]
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Oh-ho ho ho, Jeice...
When will you ever learn
you don't stand a
chance against me, huh?
[JEICE growls]
Look... I'm really tired of
wasting my time toying with you.
[JEICE growls]
[blows landing]
[JEICE screaming]
[VEGETA yells]
[JEICE shouts]
[JEICE grunts]
[JEICE coughs]
[JEICE] Huh...?
[blows landing]
[GOKU shouting]
[JEICE] Vegeta! No! Nooo!
[GOKU gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU] Vegeta! No! That kind
of violence is pointless!
[VEGETA laughs]
Thanks for the
critique, Kakarot,
but would you mind
not butting in?
So far, I've done pretty well
at looking after myself.
You see, Super Saiyans
tend to be a bit violent.
What? You're
no Super Saiyan!
[VEGETA growls]
You question me,
you body snatcher?
Huh? Well... I guess
I'll show you then...
[VEGETA yells]
[GOHAN shouts]
[blows landing]
[VEGETA yells]
What... happened?
[VEGETA] The winner!
[VEGETA laughs]
I'll get you...
That's enough, Vegeta!
He can't fight back!
[VEGETA yells]
[thinking] It's time
to change bodies!
Wha--?! He's changing!
[VEGETA laughing]
[GINYU chuckles]
Change... Now!
[both gasp]
Huh?!
[NARRATOR] Will Captain Ginyu be
able to change bodies in time
to avoid the final
blow from Vegeta?
And if so, will this be the
accidental end to our hero?
Find out in the next
exciting episode of
Dragon Ball Z!