[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the merciless Frieza
dealt the final blow
to his long-time ally,
Vegeta, the Saiyan Prince.
[NARRATOR] Miraculously, the
once cold-hearted warrior
began to overflow with emotion
as he related to Goku the cruel
circumstances under which
he became Frieza's ward.
Don't let him do this...
to anyone else...
[NARRATOR] In a passionate plea,
he begged his fellow
Saiyan to exterminate
the darkness of Frieza
once and for all.
[GOKU] Goodbye, Vegeta...
You're not as cold-hearted as
you believed yourself to be.
A heart of stone can't shed
tears like you did.
You must've been holding
them back your whole life.
[NARRATOR] In an instant,
Goku became the last surviving
Saiyan in the universe.
[NARRATOR] And with
a fiery will, he promised
to carry out Vegeta's last wish
to the best of his ability.
[NARRATOR] Full of
a new compassion
and understanding for Vegeta,
the great warrior from Earth
provided a proper burial
for his former rival.
You never had a chance
to be anything else...
It wasn't all your fault.
[NARRATOR] Though saddened
by Vegeta's passing,
Goku was more determined than
ever to take down Frieza.
The battle begins today!
[GOKU] I'll do my best to
carry out your wish!
You seem to delight in
seeing other people suffer.
And you treat life like
a disposable commodity.
[GOKU] You destroy homes...
...you take the lives of
innocent, peace-loving people...
[GOKU] You even take
the lives of children.
[GOHAN growls]
[GOKU] And all of this, for your
own amusement or personal gain.
[GOKU] Well... now
it's your turn!
Oh... Is it really? And I
suppose the great Super Saiyan
is going to arrive
and magically defeat
what has never been defeated?
It's legend... fantasy.
Who cares? Look, I don't care
about the stupid legend! See?
It's me who's
going to stop you!
[KING KAI whines]
Hey, what's up?
Well, come on, shoot.
Mmm... Vegeta... he's gone.
What?! You're kidding!
Huh?!
Man! This Frieza guy
really is unstoppable!
Yes... it's a real
pity... Yes, indeed.
But something good happened
right before Vegeta
left that world...
He told Goku that he had
been under Frieza's control
since he was a small boy.
He was in tears.
His heart was opened up.
Wow! Vegeta was crying?
No kidding? That's wack.
Yes, there is nothing more
unpredictable than life.
Change can strike
like lightning.
So what now?! I guess Goku's
on his own! Man, that bites.
Can he win?
I don't know, Tien.
He has a chance, but
it's a real slim chance.
He'll do it!
[KING KAI] Maybe, Chiaotzu...
He will!
[KING KAI] I hope so, guys...
with all my heart.
C'mon, Goku! You can do it!
[thinking] Just look at him!
He never ceases to amaze me!
I wouldn't mind fighting him
again someday, just for grins.
Huh?
Gohan, Krillin, let's go!
Now! You're distracting him!
Gohan! Let's get out of here!
Huh?!
Hey, let's get out
of here, Gohan!
You can only get in the way!
I'm leaving you, Dad!
Don't you dare lose!
Hmm...
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Raaagh!
Man, that's fast!
Blazing!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA] Hrrgh!
[GOKU] Haah!
Huh?
Oh, wow! Hey! He's missing!
He can't sense that I'm here!
Hmm...
[GOKU grunts]
Man, it's huge, huh?
--[KRILLIN] Yeah...
--[PICCOLO] Look out!
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA] Well, it was
fun while it lasted.
Huh?!
[FRIEZA growls]
Shoot! Where did
this guy come from?
How could a Saiyan
have this kind of power?
So many of them have tried,
and they all died.
Even the greatest of them
were just child's play. But this
one's different. He's fantastic!
Huh?!
[GOKU growls]
Hmm...
Hm?!
Busted!
[GOKU thinking] Okay,
settle down, Goku!
You won't be able to sense
him if you're over-anxious.
[KING KAI gasps]
Whoaa...
Hey! What? What's up now?!
Yeah! Is it Goku?
Mm-hmm...
It seems he's doing
amazingly well!
[ALL] Huh?!
You know that he almost ate
me out of house and home
when he was here?
Yes, he was highly unusual.
Like a small boy, really.
Still innocent enough to
believe that there was nothing
he couldn't do.
He's a man who has no
limits. He shuns them!
So you're saying
that he could win?
Unbelievable!
[water splashing]
[BULMA gulping]
[BULMA gasps loudly]
Oh, man, did that feel good! But
my stomach is still growling...
Oh, the pain...
[BULMA] That cloud looks
like a cheeseburger...
And that one looks
like a pizza.
I wanted to lose a few pounds,
but this is ridiculous!
Oh, I give up!
I'm just going to lie here until
I wither away! Goodbye, world...
[BULMA muffled] Hey!
Hm?
[FROGS croaking]
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA] What are you
laughing at, huh?!
[BULMA whimpers]
[BULMA squeals]
You little jerks! Can't a
girl even die in peace?!
[BULMA screams]
Huh?!
[GOKU] Uh-oh!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU shouts]
[grunting continues]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU] Haaah!
[FRIEZA] Oooh...
[GOKU squeals]
[GOKU wails]
Hmph.
Man, that smarts! Oh, yeah...
[thinking] Hm... I think he's
trying to make a fool of me.
Catch this, monkey!
Hmmm...?
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] Whoa! Big one!
Huh...?
[GOKU] Uh-oh!
[GOKU] Man! This whole
planet is coming apart!
Huh?!
[FRIEZA cackles]
[GOHAN] Man, what the heck
is going on over there?!
[KRILLIN] I don't know,
but I bet it's not good!
It feels like the whole
planet's gonna blow!
Dad...
No! You've got to have faith
in your dad, Gohan! He's fine!
But if you show up,
he'll be vulnerable!
Come on, Dad...
Goku...
[GOKU] Yikes!
Oops!
Whoa, man, that's really deep!
Whoa!
Wow! Towering walls of
molten lava! This isn't good!
This planet is
completely unstable!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU yells]
The end.
Huh?!
[GOKU shouts]
[GOKU screams]
[FRIEZA] A pity, really.
Such an uneventful ending.
And for such a great fighter.
Hey, what have you done
to him?! Where is he?!
[FRIEZA] Where is who?
[PICCOLO] You know who
I'm talking about!
Oh, yes! I seem to recall him
melting in the river of lava.
How would you like to join him?
I'm making a stew down there
and I wouldn't mind adding
a Namek for seasoning.
Yes, that's just what it needs.
Perfect! Consider it done.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOKU sighs]
That was close!
Man, you could get a wicked
heat-rash from that!
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU yelping]
Oh! Mama! Yow!
[FRIEZA} Whatd'ya say,
Namek? Are you ready? I am.
Ai-yai-yai-yai! Whoa!
[GOKU screams]
Hm?!
[GOKU screaming]
My butt's on fire!
Yes!
Hyaah!
Hrrgh!
[GOKU growling]
[growling continues]
[GOKU] Man, I hope
that patch holds!
Phew...
Hey! Goku! Look out!
[GOKU] Hey, just what's
your deal anyway, Frieza?
[FRIEZA] Basically,
I'm trying to kill you.
[GOKU] Then leave this
planet out of our fight!
Got it? Let it be!
[FRIEZA] Hmph.
Okay, have it your way.
[GOKU] Fine! Then it's agreed!
[FRIEZA] I've never met a
sentimental Saiyan before.
It'll be your downfall.
[GOKU] Well, if having
feelings is a weakness,
why am I the only Saiyan left?
[NARRATOR] The battle between
Goku and Frieza continues
on the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!