[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta was attacked from within
by Babidi's dark magic,
and by the hatred from his past.
[SUPREME KAI] Fight it,
Vegeta! You must resist!
[NARRATOR] Discovering the
evil thoughts still buried
deep in Vegeta's heart,
Babidi quickly manipulated them
to his own advantage.
All the bitterness,
hurt, and anger
that had ruled Vegeta long ago
were brought to the surface.
It consumed him.
And put him under
Babidi's control.
Once finished,
the wizard took no time
in putting his new
slave to the test.
Cruelly transporting
the Z Fighters back
to the World Tournament Arena,
where Vegeta could
attack his friends
while endangering
thousands of innocent lives.
And at the same
time, gather energy
for Majin Buu's revival.
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR] Vegeta fired
a powerful energy blast
that not even
Goku could deflect.
And as the Saiyan hero
was thrown to the side,
Vegeta's attack made a direct
hit on the audience nearby.
The Z Fighters could
only watch in horror,
as nothing but cinders remained.
[NARRATOR] It was difficult
to believe that this gruesome
human catastrophe had been
caused by one of their own.
[GOKU]
Shame on you.
[NARRATOR] But despite
Babidi's commands to destroy
all the Z Fighters,
Vegeta wants only one thing.
It has plagued his
mind ever since
the days of Frieza,
but will his deepest desire
at last be realized?
The long-awaited
fight against Goku?!
[CROWD screaming]
[screaming continues]
[whimpers]
No! Don't do this!
Please, don't do it!
Oh man. I've never
seen this side.
But I know that look
he's got all too well.
Oh, he can't possibly
be doing this! Not now!
[cackles]
[GOTEN] So what do you
think this "Buu" monster
Videl told us about is like?
I don't know, Goten,
I just hope our dads
have survived him!
What?! They won't?!!
Calm down.
I was just saying
it was a possibility.
But Gohan and my
dad are real strong.
Oh, and they say
your dad's okay, too.
He is! He is! He is! He is!
He is! He is! He is!
And they're all gonna
make sphagetti out of Buu!
Yeah?
Then we better get there fast
so we can see 'im first!
[GOTEN]
That's right!
[BABIDI cackling]
Fabulous!
You see?! The chaos
has just been doubled!
[MR. SATAN whimpering]
What should we
do now, Mr. Satan?
Why in the world
are you askin' me?
[YELLING GUY 1]
Help us, Mr. Satan!
What are you waiting for?!
Take him out!
[YELLER]
Yeah! Mister Satan!
[MR. SATAN gasping]
Well, they're right.
You're... the champ!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
He's right!
I can't let my fans down!
I've got a responsibility!
I've got tickets to sell!
I'm the hope of the world!
Hey! Maniac!
I'm afraid I can't allow you
to move another inch!
Your crime spree will
end at my glorious fists!
You've come head to head with
the champion of
the world, big guy!
[laughs]
Hey, why are you laughing?
[laughing]
I'm the champ...
It isn't working.
[MR. SATAN growls]
On second thought,
fighting you amateurs
would be too much of a joke!
So, here's what I
think we should do!
You seem to have
unresolved issues!
I say you two fight for an
exhausting amount of time
and then I'll take on
whatever's le--
Quiet!
[BOTH whimper]
How 'bout it? Shall we commence?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[GOKU]
This isn't the time, Vegeta.
You'll fight with me, Kakarot.
Unless of course you'd
like more bodies
to pile up on your conscience.
[GOKU gasps]
Vegeta...
Certainly you didn't...
[laughs]
How sad...
I didn't figure you were
weak enough to be controlled.
[gasps]
[GOHAN]
Dad... don't...
Answer me! Vegeta!
Do you let yourself be a slave?!
[gasps]
[yells]
[CROWD screams]
[VEGETA]
Tell me!
Is it slavery when
you get what you want?
[ANNOUNCER, MR. SATAN gasping]
[gasps]
[VEGETA cackles]
[GOKU grunting, growling]
Stop it! You don't know
what you're doing!
[growls]
Stand aside!
This does not concern you!
It's between me and your
circus clown of a father!
Circus clown...
Well, that's a new one.
[VEGETA cackles]
[SUPREME KAI]
No, Goku! You mustn't!
If you fight him here,
you will be doing
precisely what Babidi wishes!
Every injury that Vegeta causes
will be sent back to the ship!
And Buu will be revived!
[GOKU]
Tell me, Vegeta...
With that stamp on your
head I know Babidi's
been giving you orders.
Is this one of them?
Are you trying to fight me
because of him,
or is this the same old
story between you and me?
Which one?
Does it really matter?
Not to you, Gohan, but to
a warrior, it matters greatly.
And you know what this
as well as I do, Kakarot.
In a day, you'll be
back to the dead,
and I will not miss
this opportunity!
Who are you people?!
Don't you see the
universe matters
more than your
meaningless squabble?
[growls] Meaningless, huh?
[gasps]
What do you know of meaningless?
Spend most of your life
ruled by another!
Watch your race
dwindle to a handful!
And then...
Tell me what has more meaning
than your own strength!
I have in me the blood
of a Saiyan Prince...
He is nothing but a joke!
Yet I've had to watch him
surpass me in strength!
My destiny...
thrown to the wayside!
He-He's even saved my life
as if I were a helpless child!
He has stolen my honor,
and his debts...
...must be paid!
[GOKU]
Babidi!
Transport us to a place
away from people!
If you give me that,
then I will fight Vegeta!
Ha!
[BABIDI]
See! I've done it!
[cackles] Now they'll
crumble from the inside!
So be it!
[grunts]
If you truly believe this
is the right decision...
...then you will have to
get around me to do it!
[GOKU]
Don't do this, Supreme Kai.
[SUPREME KAI] Goku...
I'm afraid I have no choice.
[GOKU]
Then neither do I.
[GOHAN gasps]
[gasps]
Dad, you can't!
[SUPREME KAI]
Fine. Do what you will.
I can't stop you.
[GOKU]
I'm sorry, Supreme Kai.
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes... So am I.
[cackling]
[BABIDI] Oh! See them go
at each other's throats!
Serves you right, Kai!
Now it is a simple
game of waiting...
And Majin Buu will return.
[BABIDI cackling] I'll move
them. It's a small price to pay!
Papparapa!
[ANNOUNCER]
Huh? That's weird.
They're gone again!
Just flat disappeared!
How do they keep doing that?
[laughs] That's a pity!
And here I was just
about to go over
and take them all on
at the same time! Darn!
I trust you'll have
no more excuses.
None.
Dad, don't do this!
[SUPREME KAI]
It's all right.
There's no point resisting
what cannot be helped...
We will just have to
continue our efforts
with a new strategy.
While you two fight up here,
Gohan and I will break open
the ship's entrance and
continue our assault
against Babidi and Dabura.
I believe we still
have a chance
at stopping them
before Buu's revival.
If tampering with the ship's
entrance ruptures Buu's shell,
it will still be better
than allowing him
to reach full power
from the energy lost by Goku.
After all the time I've
spent tracking Majin Buu,
I will avert him
with my own hands.
Oh, no you don't!
You're forgetting what I can do!
Vegeta! Destroy this nuisance!
Kill the Supreme Kai!
Kill him!
[VEGETA grunting]
[BABIDI] The only way is
to kill the Supreme Kai!
Yes! Kill him, Vegeta!
[VEGETA grunting, yelling]
[gasps]
[VEGETA grunting, groaning]
Babidi's entered his mind!
[BABIDI] You can't afford
to let him live, Vegeta!
[VEGETA screams]
[VEGETA groaning]
[BABIDI]
Kill him, Vegeta! Kill him!
I refuse.
What?!
Huh?
Your business with the Kai.
It means nothing to me!
Kakarot is my only objective.
That's amusing, Vegeta
but I'm serious.
By every fiber in your body,
I command you to destroy!
[VEGETA grunting]
Kill... Kill the Kai!
[VEGETA]
N-No. Get out of my head!
I already told you!
I... will not...
...be distracted from
this anymore! I won't!
It will take more than
head games to stop me.
You may have invaded
my mind and my body,
but there's one thing
a Saiyan always keeps!
His pride!
[VEGETA yells]
[BABIDI grunts, yells]
[VEGETA panting]
But-But this has never
happened to me before!
Since when can the possessed
say no to the possessor?!
It doesn't make any
difference, Babidi.
Just remember...
His purpose is to steal
energy for Majin Buu.
So why not let him
have his way, for now?
We will only have
the Supreme Kai
and the boy to worry about,
and I've already
shown I can handle them.
This way, you'll see the
Supreme Kai die at your feet
just as you had intended.
I can't believe it...
What kind of strength allows
a person to fight against
and overpower their
own enslaved body?
I guess I've been
keeping you waiting
for a long time, Vegeta.
But no more.
[DABURA]
Master, may I make a suggestion?
[BABIDI] Go ahead, Dabura.
But it better be good.
I'm feeling temperamental.
Let's open the doors for them...
That way we won't run the risk
of Buu's seal rupturing
before he's complete, and
besides I'd like to get my hands
on that boy as soon as I can.
Dabura... I think...
I won't kill you.
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[GOHAN]
They're opening the ship for us!
[SUPREME KAI]
Careful, Gohan.
We must be watchful of traps.
Alright, Dad. I guess I'm off.
Take care, Gohan.
I don't have to tell
you there's a lot
riding on this, so do your best.
Here. We've got two
Senzu Beans left.
I want you to take one.
You'll need to be
at full strength for
whatever happens down there.
Thanks. I'll do what I can.
Don't worry, son.
You've got all the power
you need to beat these guys.
Just remember how to
fight with your feelings
like you did against Cell.
Yeah... But how?
Just remember about all the
people you're fighting for
and how much you
care about them.
And then let that
be your weapon.
I've... I've missed
hearing you Dad...
It's a shame this one day for
you to be back had to get
so screwed up, but I'm
glad that you're here.
[GOHAN]
Let's go!
I'm ready now.
That's good to hear.
So, Kakarot...
The table has been set.
Now, let us begin!
[GOKU] The more time you
and I spend fighting,
the more damage I'll
receive to fuel Majin Buu.
So if it's all right with you,
let's just skip the warm-up.
By all means.
I just hope that
being dead this long
hasn't made your body fragile.
[growls]
[yells]
[VEGETA]
Well, at least you're stronger
than your son was against Cell.
[yells]
[gasps]
Wow, Vegeta...
This might take
longer than I thought.
You see! This is
our fate! Our battle!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR]
And so it has been decided.
Against the wishes
of the Supreme Kai...
Against the commands
of the wizard Babidi...
Goku and Vegeta have marked
off their battlefield,
and the last two survivors
of the Saiyan race
will embark in the
ultimate fight.
Next time, on Dragon Ball Z.