[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
the elder Kai gave Goku an
empowered set of earrings,
allowing him to perform
an instant, effortless fusion.
But, there was a catch.
Whoever wore the
matching earring
would fuse with him forever.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[NARRATOR] Back on Earth,
the super-charged Majin Buu
tried to destroy the
remaining survivors
with one, terrifying blast.
But thanks to a timely arrival
by the revitalized Goku,
Buu's attempts were cut short.
[NARRATOR]
Down but far from out,
Majin Buu quickly
incapacitated Tien,
who had returned from seclusion
to play his small part.
[GOKU]
He was off guard!
[NARRATOR]
And pulling himself together,
Majin Buu readied to battle
Goku head to head,
with powers that not even the
great Saiyan hero could stop.
[GOKU]
Here! Catch!
[NARRATOR]
Aware of the desperate odds,
Goku threw the Kai's
earring to Gohan,
deciding to save the Earth
by merging permanently
with his son.
But Gotenks' fusion wore off
inside Buu's body,
causing a sharp drop
in the monster's power.
Goku chose at the last minute
not to go through
with the fusion.
And that's when
Buu made his move.
[GOKU]
Gohan!
[NARRATOR] Just as he had done
with Piccolo and Gotenks,
Majin Buu absorbed
Gohan into his body,
and gained his incredible power.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Now, Goku must convince
someone else to fuse with him.
A task that may prove
very, very difficult.
[laughs]
[GOKU grunting]
[SUPER BUU] So, what're
you going to do now?!
Think, Goku! Both of your
sons are a part of me now.
Maybe we should seek
family counseling?
[laughs]
[GOKU]
Poor Tien...
[GOKU] Man, I've got to
find some more power!
[SUPER BUU] You know they all
resent you for leaving, Goku.
They're telling me.
That won't work on me!
You're the monster who devoured
everyone we care about!
[laughs]
Yes, I suppose I did, but you
were supposed to stop me.
[growls]
Oh, don't take it
too personally, Goku.
Everybody fails.
Your failure just means
the end of the world!
Don't worry,
if I get a chance, I'll get
rid of that creep for good!
Well, only one problem.
I don't have any bullets left.
Pretty lucky for Buu, huh?!
Yes, lucky him.
Tell you what I'm going to do.
I'll give you a chance to
join bodies with someone.
[gasps]
You have until the count of five
to find a suitable partner,
so get moving!
One!
[gasps]
Two!
[GOKU thinking] No, Dende's
size would hurt more than help.
Besides, we need him
for the Dragon Balls!
[SUPER BUU]
Three!
[GOKU] Oh man, Mr. Satan's
not exactly a warrior.
His lack of understanding
about energy could hurt, too,
but, he does know
basic martial arts.
Four!
I've got no choice!
Hey, you!
Huh?!
[GOKU]
Put this on!
[GOKU thinking]
What's that?!
That energy...
[GOKU thinking]
He's here!
This is as far as I go.
I'm sorry we're not closer,
but I've got my health
to think about, you know!
Heh/ That's fine, we can
wait here for now.
I'm sure Buu will
find me soon enough.
[SUPER BUU]
And five!
Yeah, yeah!
[SUPER BUU]
What is that fool doing?
He hasn't even
tried to fuse yet!
Too bad!
[yells]
Yeah!
[grunts]
Coward, where are you hiding?!
[BABA]
I'm outta here!
[VEGETA]
Hm?!
[GOKU]
Vegeta?!
All right! It's you! I knew it!
[gasps] Kakarot!
Goku!
Hi!
What happened to your halo?
[OLD KAI]
Very interesting development.
Yes, I should've
seen this coming.
Look! It's-It's Vegeta.
Ah, what good luck!
If those two join bodies,
they will be a force
to be reckoned with.
[SUPREME KAI]
But Vegeta, sometime earlier,
he destroyed his body in
an attempt to stop Majin Buu.
How is it he has returned
to the living world?
King Yemma must have seen
the situation and intervened.
Yemma may look like
a brainless bear,
but he does have his moments.
[OLD KAI laughs]
[SUPER BUU] Does he really
think he can escape me?
[SUPER BUU laughs]
I'll hunt him down,
no matter how far he goes.
After all, I don't
have anything else to do!
--[MR. SATAN groaning]
--[BEE barks]
[DENDE]
That's it, he's gone.
Hey buddy, did you see what that
guy was trying to throw to me?
What a time to try
to get an autograph!
That was the strangest thing.
Sorry, I can't talk right now.
I've gotta find a way
to improve this situation.
Hey!
Wait, don't leave me here alone!
I saved your life,
remember? You owe me!
[barks]
Uh? What happened
to you, Goku?
The halo on your
head has disappeared.
You've come back to life!
Uh? Oh yeah! That's
kind of a long story,
but basically this Old Kai
gave me his own life, and um--
Ah! [growls]
Darn! Majin Buu's coming.
He must be getting very
anxious to fight with me!
Baba, you'd better get out
of here while you still can.
Uh, sure, yes. Good idea.
I'll be rooting for you two
boys from a safe distance!
Okay! Ah, good-bye!
I don't know if you're
gonna believe this,
but boy am I glad to see you.
I've got a plan
to beat Majin Buu,
and with your help, I know
we can make it work, Vegeta!
[VEGETA grunts]
Put this on, right now.
I know it sounds strange, but ya
have to do it. Please, hurry.
What for?
'Cause, once you put this on,
you and I will be able
to combine bodies!
Fusion?
[GOKU]
That's right, think about it!
You and I joined in one body!
We'll have amazing strength!
[chuckles]
Sorry, the offer's tempting,
but I decline.
That's not an option!
[SUPER BUU]
What's this? Another fighter?
[laughs]
Go on, try your precious fusion!
That won't save you
from me, not now!
Come on! This is no time for us
to argue! We have to do this!
Get away from me, Kakarot!
I'd rather lose my body than
have anything to do with you!
[groans]
[grunts]
[SUPER BUU laughing]
I found you!
Here he comes!
Listen to me, Vegeta,
we've tried this!
You can't beat him like that!
[grunts]
This is the only chance we have!
Really? And just why
should I believe you?
[VEGETA grunts]
Out of my way!
[yells]
[SUPER BUU, VEGETA chuckle]
It's you, I remember
fighting with you before.
[SUPER BUU]
You're not the one I'm after,
but I'll be glad
to destroy you both!
[SUPER BUU yells]
[BEE pants]
[DENDE] Hang on, Tien,
I'm going to heal you!
[gasps]
There, that's better!
[MR. SATAN sputters]
You saved me, thanks Dende.
Where's Goku?
And where's Buu?
Goku left somewhere,
Instant Transmission,
and Majin Buu followed him.
[TIEN]
I see.
[MR. SATAN] Uh. Hey, uh, how
come, uh, he's, uh, good again?
[SUPER BUU] Come on,
why don't you attack me?
It's two against one!
[GOKU]
Cool it, Vegeta!
You've got to understand
that Buu's powers
have increased a lot
since you last fought.
There's no way that you can win!
You think he's the most
powerful being in the universe,
and maybe he is,
but just like you,
he does not have true pride!
[growls]
I don't expect you to
understand. Not you, Kakarot!
I sent myself into a cold
oblivion, and I did it on a lie!
The Saiyan Prince
will not fall again!
[yells]
[yelling continues]
[SUPER BUU screams]
[gasps]
[growls]
No, don't!
[VEGETA grunting]
[roars]
--[SUPER BUU grunting]
--[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunting]
Let go of me!
[yells]
[VEGETA] Do not help me,
Kakarot! Do not help me!
[SUPER BUU]
Well, it would seem you two
have some issues to work out!
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[groans]
[VEGETA grunts]
[yells]
[VEGETA groaning]
[chuckles]
[GOKU]
Listen to me, Vegeta!
You see, you can't
fight him on your own.
There's only one
thing left to do.
I don't know why
you're so angry,
but time's running out!
[GOKU]
You have to let it go.
Vegeta!
Quiet!
Look, they're fighting, again.
They had better
hurry up and fuse
before Majin Buu
sucks up another one.
What's wrong with those
two youths, anyway?
Do they have a grudge
against each other?
Uh, yes!
I suppose this canyon here
will make a good
cemetery for them both.
Come on Vegeta, we don't
have much time left!
Please, you've got to
help me, just this once!
You want my help?!
[GOKU grunts]
You've got some nerve,
asking me to help you!
You still don't think I
know what you did to me?
[gasps]
I have traveled
to the Other World
I know all about your technique.
Your Super Saiyan Three.
You hid it from
me during our battle.
You allowed me to believe
that I could beat you!
Yeah, that's part true.
I do have the ability to
become a Super Saiyan Three.
But hey, I can only
do it for a short time!
Ah! That's enough of
your lies! Pride-less!
Do you not realize
my humiliation!
Just stay away from me!
I hope that you two are
done fighting each other.
Because now it's my turn
to have a little fun!
[yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[yells]
[GOKU]
He's coming back!
[VEGETA, GOKU yell]
[yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH grunt]
[SUPER BUU laughs]
Darn it! I told you
this was impossible!
[GOKU] Look, if we don't
do something soon,
we'll be history!
Along with this whole planet.
Why do I care?
Wake up! Majin Buu's eaten
everyone we care about.
Everyone is gone!
Even Bulma!
[gasps]
[grunts]
They've become part of Buu.
They can't even die!
I just thought
the least we could do
is put our old differences
aside, just this once,
and really work together.
We owe that to our teammates,
our families, Vegeta,
our friends.
[KRILLIN screams]
[ALL scream]
[GOKU] Look, you've always
talked about our Saiyan race.
How we're the last
of a mighty people.
Well, it's time we accept
we're starting a new race,
one that can be just
as strong, just as proud,
but not if we're caught up in
so much of our old birthrights
to see what we have
right in front of us!
We've lost our old race, Vegeta.
Let's not lose this one, too!
[VEGETA]
Kakarot,
how do you know this fusion
will be enough to stop him?
I don't know for sure,
but I know it's the best chance
we have of saving the Earth!
[gasps]
You two have lived long enough!
[yells]
Here, give it to me!
Ah!
What are you waiting for?
Give it now!
You bet!
It's time to die!
Come on, you said
right ear, right?
That's right Vegeta,
and one more thing,
once we join our bodies we'll
be stuck in that form, forever.
[gasps] Imbecile!
You tell me now?
Don't you think that's
important information?
To the end of Earth!
All right! It's on!
Great! Thanks, Vegeta.
[laughing]
[VEGETA grunts]
[laughs, gasps]
[gasps]
All right! Ha, ha, ha!
[NARRATOR]
Unbelievable!
Goku and Vegeta have put
aside their differences,
and fused into one warrior!
A new page in Z-Fighter
history has been turned,
but how will they fare
in the fight against Buu?