[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Mister Satan and Number 18
went one on one
to see who would be crowned
the new World Champion!
Mister Satan was wishing
that he had wings
until 18 made him a
surprising offer!
In exchange for
20,000,000 zeni,
18 agreed to take a dive and
let Mister Satan win the title,
even though she was clearly
the superior fighter!
[MR. SATAN] And you really
think you have what it takes
to tame the king of the jungle?!
[NARRATOR]
With his victory secured,
Mister Satan was once again
at his boastful best!
[MR. SATAN]
Comin' at you, sweetheart!
No more foolin' around!
Feel my true power!
[NARRATOR] For 18,
Mister Satan's Megaton Punch
was child's play, but her own
greed had her on the ground
and out of the match!
The contest was over!
The crowd was delighted
to again see their hero
take home the title.
But even as the World
Martial Arts Tournament
drew to a close, elsewhere,
another test of strength
was about to begin!
[SUPREME KAI]
It's Dabura!
[NARRATOR] Babidi has sent
the King of the Demon World
to face the Z-Warriors
at Stage Three...
[DEBURA] ...which means, none of
you will progress any further
[NARRATOR] There can be no
taking a dive in this match!
In this contest, money means
nothing, survival is everything!
And Gohan is intent
on doing just that!
[NARRATOR] Staying alive
in a fight against Dabura
is something that no mortal
has ever managed to do before!
[DABURA laughs]
[NARRATOR] Then again,
Dabura has never faced
a mortal quite like Gohan!
It's good versus the King of
Evil, today on Dragon Ball Z!
[growls]
[VEGETA] Finally! Now we'll
get to see a real test!
Let's see how this Dabura fellow
does against a Super Saiyan!
Yeah!
It always makes things more
interesting, that's for sure!
What?!
[groans]
[groans, yells]
[yells]
[BABIDI]
Ahh... What astounding power
that young man has!
Oh, no! Dabura!
[DABURA grunts]
[DABURA, GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN yells]
[DABURA grunts]
Come on, Dabura!
Show your true power!
You can't win at this rate!
[growls]
Oh! Amazing!
[GOKU] Hm! You haven't
seen anything yet!
[GOHAN]
Well, what about it, Dabura?
[chuckles] You want a
glimpse of my true power?!
Well, so be it!
I didn't know you were
in such a hurry to die!
[yells]
[cackles]
[DABURA grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[DABURA, GOHAN grunting]
[DABURA growls]
[GOHAN yells]
[DABURA, GOHAN grunting]
[DABURA growls]
[GOHAN grunts]
[DABURA]
Looking... for... me?!
Oh, no!
[GOHAN groans]
[GOKU, SUPREME KAI gasp]
[BABIDI]
Oh, my! Yes!
Nice work, Dabura! One down!
Excellent!
[GOHAN thinking]
He's waiting for me!
[DABURA]
Hm...
[GOHAN grunts]
[grunts]
Hm? What's this?
[DABURA]
There!
[GOHAN yelps]
Gohan!
[GOHAN panting]
[laughs] Is that all the power
your transformation yields?!
You're pathetic!
[SUPREME KAI] Dabura is far
stronger than Yakon and Pui Pui!
[GOKU]
That's okay. So's Gohan.
[GOHAN grunts]
All right, then! Round two!
Let's do it! Whenever
you're ready, big guy!
[laughs]
[DABURA, GOHAN grunt]
[GOHAN, DABURA grunt]
What does Gohan
think he's doing?
A direct attack won't
work on this guy...
He should know
better than that...
[VEGETA] This is what happens
when you don't train
for seven years! He's completely
lost his fighting sense.
Pitiful.
Hm! Not bad!
[chuckles]
[DABURA]
Come on!
If you dare!
All right!
[yells]
Gohan! Be careful!
Don't let it hit you!
Wha...?! Ahh!
What the--?
[DABURA]
Mm?
[grunts]
[laughs] Whew!
Talk about your lucky break!
[CROWD cheers]
[yells]
[ANNOUNCER]
There he is!
The Champion of the World
for yet another year,
the one and only, Mister Satan!
What a powerhouse!
Amazing! And he's as
fast as he is strong!
Nobody deserved the title as
much as this man did here today!
What a guy!
A true champion indeed!
[CHICHI]
Goten?!
[BULMA]
Trunks?! Where are you two?!
[CHICHI] Goten! You better
not be hiding again!
[MARON] Hey, look!
It's my mommy! Hi, Mommy!
I missed you...
Sorry you lost...
Did it hurt when he
punched you in the face?
Not really, little one.
No way!
What happened?! I can't
believe that creep won!
The whole crowd thought
you lost on purpose
until he explained about
that delayed punch!
[ANDROID 18]
Hm?
Why would I lose on purpose?
[BULMA]
I didn't say that!
I said they thought
you lost on purpose!
[BULMA]
Let's go, Maron!
[MARON]
Okay!
Well, what the heck's her deal!
I know that she would
never lose on purpose!
Give me a break!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Woo-hoo! Yay!
We get to see the wizard!
Hey, Trunks?
What is it, Goten?
What's a wizard?
Huh?!
[GOTEN]
Hmm?!
[TRUNKS] Goten, has anyone
told you you're stupid?
[GOTEN]
Huh? What'd I do?!
You got all excited!
Now you're saying you don't
even know what a wizard is!
Uh-huh. But that's okay!
You know so you
can tell me, right?!
Well... Yeah.
Sure I can! Are you
sure you wanna know?
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
[TRUNKS]
Well, uh...
Promise not to tell?
[GOTEN]
Yeah, yeah! Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Well, all right. Hmm...
I'm ready!
Hmm... Uuhhh...
Well a wizard is...
He's kinda like a...
a...
Wizard is a word that
rhymes with lizard!
See?!
And a Wizard is like a
lizard turned into a man!
Wow! I can't wait!
Yeah, me either!
Huh?
[TRUNKS]
Ahh! What am I worried about?
I'm the Champion of the World!
[DABURA, GOHAN grunting]
Huh?!
[DABURA]
I feel your power decreasing!
It's only a matter of time
before you make a mistake!
[GOHAN]
What if you make one first?
[DABURA cackles]
I wouldn't count on it!
[GOKU]
Hm.
This Dabura guy's giving
Gohan a lot more trouble
than I thought he would...
Bah!
He's tough, but he's
not unbeatable!
Gohan's gotten soft!
He was a lot stronger
when he was a little kid!
It's absurd!
Yeah he's definitely
slacked off!
Well, at least he got straight
A's on his report card!
[growls] I could beat Dabura!
[DABURA]
Hmm? Hm?!
[GOHAN]
Mistake number one!
[yells]
[DABURA groans]
Sword!
[DABURA]
Taste my blade!
[gasps]
Ahh! I think he's
got him this time!
[DABURA cackles]
Hm?!
[DABURA]
What?!
[laughs]
[growls]
[BABIDI]
What?!
Dabura's caused hardly
any damage at all!
He's going to have to
do better than this
or Buu will never be ready!
Ahh... But once he is...
Oh, yes...!
He'll kill them all!
[yells]
[DEBURA cackling]
[GOHAN grunts]
[DABURA grunts]
[DABURA, GOHAN grunting]
[DABURA yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
[DABURA grunts]
--[GOHAN grunts]
--[DABURA groans]
[DABURA grunting]
[gasps]
[DABURA grunts]
[VEGETA thinking]
Come on! Come on, already!
[DABURA yells]
[GOHAN gasps]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[growls]
[GOHAN grunting]
[yells]
[DABURA growls]
[panting]
[VEGETA]
I can't take this anymore!
This is ridiculous!
Why are we subjecting
ourselves to this?!
Look! Call him down,
Kakarot! I'll finish this!
Just give him a
little more time!
It's not like he's
completely lost yet!
Why not let him fight?
He's hangin' in there!
Dabura's toying with him!
You know that! Come on!
[DABURA]
Hmm?
[VEGETA]
Why should I sit around all day
acting like this matters?!
I could end this in five
minutes if I wanted to!
I'm not here to
play games, Kakarot!
Or to create nice
father-son memories!
I'm here to win!
Stop pretending! Knock off
the sentimental rubbish!
The strongest one is the
one who should do the job!
I'm the one who should
be fighting, not him!
Huh?
[DABURA thinking]
Master!
Please bring us back to
the ship immediately!
I have made an
important discovery!
A discovery, Dabura?
Yes, it's vital to our plans.
I think you'll agree.
Very well, then!
But it better be a good
one to interrupt a fight!
[DABURA]
It is, Master.
[BABIDI] So you're ready
to return right now?
Yes.
[BABIDI]
Okay. Papparapa!
[DABURA laughs]
[GOHAN gasps]
[VEGETA]
What?! What are we doing here?!
[GOKU]
I don't know!
I guess they wanted us back
on the ship for some reason!
But why?!
[GOHAN]
Hey!
Where do ya think
you're going?!
Are you giving up, or what?!
[DABURA] Oh, no! It's just
a brief intermission!
We just need a few minutes
to rework our stategy!
It seems we've
found a new recruit!
The perfect warrior, capable
of handling all of you!
So just take a little rest
while we bring him up to speed!
[laughs]
Hey! Come back!
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
What are they up to?!
They don't have any warriors
stronger than Dabura!
Welcome back!
Now then. What's this
that you were saying?
Did you really make
a discovery?! Hmm?
[DABURA chuckles]
Yes!
[BABIDI]
Good.
I was beginning to think
that you'd lost your nerve,
and were just looking for
an excuse to get away.
But I guess I
was wrong, wasn't I?
[DABURA] Mmm. The Demon King
fears no mortal!
Although I admit, they were
stronger than I thought.
Well! I'm glad to hear it!
Now! About this
discovery of yours.
Why don't you fill
me in, please.
I saw that one of the
mortals has a terrible
rage burning in his heart...
He lacks the conviction
of the others.
He could be made to
serve our purposes...
You're kidding me!
Now I know what you're thinking!
We can revive Buu
and defeat them all
without even lifting a finger!
Brilliant, Dabura! Ha, ha, haa!
I'm here to please you,
my master.
[BABIDI]
You are priceless!
Here comes the Buu!
[BABADI cackles]
[DABURA chuckles]
[NARRATOR] What foul plan
are the evil Dabura
and Babidi concocting?
Gohan and the others
are ready for anything
that comes at them, but is the
real enemy lurking within?!
Can Babidi really bring
one of the Z-fighters
under his control?
Find out next Dragon Ball Z!