[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Cell became obsessed
with a new goal.
Having learned of Gohan's
incredible dormant power,
he was now determined
to bring it out.
[NARRATOR] It was a painful
process of trial and error,
as the mighty Cell made
several varied attempts.
[CELL laughs]
[NARRATOR] Trapping Gohan
in a powerful death lock,
Cell tried to
lure the boy's power
with a heavy treatment of pain.
[CELL] Do it!
[NARRATOR] Goku had been
confident of his son's ability
ever since they stepped out of
the Hyperbolic Time Chamber.
But as the Saiyan hero
watched his son
being tortured on
the battlefield,
he realized
he had made a mistake.
He would have to step
in and stop Cell himself.
[NARRATOR] But beating
Goku to the punch
was the silent giant Android 16,
whose attempt to stop
Cell was quickly shattered.
along with his metal body.
And seeing Gohan's reaction
to the android's death
gave Cell a new strategy.
[CELL] So, Gohan, we still
haven't gotten you mad.
Let's try some
friendly persuasion.
[NARRATOR] And then the
unthinkable happened.
Cell spawned
from his tail
seven miniature
versions of himself
to attack the Z Fighters.
With the hopes that
watching his friends in pain
would cause Gohan to
unleash his hidden strength.
[CELL] Now, my dear children.
Those seven on the
cliff are your enemies!
Give them pain.
Kill them if it makes you happy!
[GOHAN gasps]
Hop to it!
[NARRATOR] How will Goku
and the others
fair against these
frightening creatures?
Will this be the key to
triggering Gohan's power?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball Z!
[CELL JRs. whooping &amp; yelling]
[YAMCHA gasps] No!
[VEGETA yells]
[TRUNKS growls]
[TIEN growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOKU growls]
[whooping &amp; yelling continues]
[laughing]
[VEGETA growls]
[grunting]
--[CELL JR. 1 chuckles]
--[VEGETA gasps]
[CELL JR. 2 raspberries]
[CELL JR. 2 laughs]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[yelling]
You missed me!
[KRILLIN growls]
[yelling]
[CELL JR. 2 giggles]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[blows landing]
[VEGETA yells]
[TIEN grunts]
[KRILLIN grunting,
CELL JR. 2 giggling]
[YAMCHA grunts,
blows landing]
[GOKU growls]
[CELL JR. 7 squeals]
--[CELL JR. 7 yells]
--[blows landing]
[various grunting,
blows landing]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Oh! The unknown band of
fighters are being pummeled
by these new
little monsters!
Everyone is
fighting at once
in an all-out punching frenzy!
No rules! No order!
And no hope for any of us!
Unless, of course...
Mr. Satan, how is it?
Huh?!
[ANNOUNCER] Your dreadful
stomach virus! How is it?!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
You know, just because
I don't scream and whine
about it all the
time like a little sissy,
doesn't mean that it's still
isn't threatening my life!
Oh, well of course not!
A stomach pain like this
would have killed
any normal man!
I'm the only
guy in the world
with the strength to bear it!
Wow! That's very impressive!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
So... it still hurts?
[MR. SATAN] Uhh...
Owchy owchy owchy!
Oh, the terrible pain!
Make it stop!
[PIIZA] I still have some
of that medicine, Hercule!
[MR. SATAN] Oh, uh no! Too much
pain to swallow anything!
[CELL JR. 7 screams]
[GOKU growls,
CELL JR. 7 grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[CELL JR. yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
Goku!
[CELL JR. 2 growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[growling]
[PICCOLO yells]
Hey, Yamcha! Tien!
Goku is still worn out
from his fight with Cell!
[CELL JR. 4 yells]
We have to protect him!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[CELL JR. 4 screams]
Yamcha, duck!
--[CELL JR. 6 gasps]
--[PICCOLO grunts]
[CELL JR. 6 screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[CELL JR. 7 giggles]
[shouting]
Oh?
[CELL JR. 7 gasps]
[yelling]
[CELL JR. 7 screams]
[CELL JR. 4 groans]
[CELL JR. 5 giggles]
[TIEN &amp; YAMCHA grunt]
Thanks, you guys.
Hey, there's no need to
thank us. We're a team.
[CELL JRs. growl, giggle]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[CELL JR. 3 laughs]
[TRUNKS growls]
[VEGETA &amp; CELL JR. 1 grunting]
[KRILLIN &amp; CELL JR. 2 grunting]
[CELL JR. 2 laughs]
[PICCOLO growls]
Nice save!
[CELL JR. 6 groans]
[blows landing]
[CELL JR. 6 grunts]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[grunting]
Get up, Krillin!
[CELL JR. 6 yells]
[KRILLIN screams]
[GOHAN gasps]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[thinking] I-I can't let
those monsters kill them!
Most of them can't
be wished back to life!
They'll just be gone!
They'll all be gone!
--[CELL JR. 4 growls]
--[YAMCHA grunts]
--[CELL JR. 5 squeals]
--[TIEN yells]
[GOHAN gasps]
[PICCOLO grunting,
CELL JR. 7 giggling]
[GOHAN growls]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[CELL JR. 2 grunts]
[laughing]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Aahh, your energy
is beginning to swell.
That's good.
Now take your anger
and feed off of it!
Use it to unleash
your power
before it's too late
for your friends.
Just take a look out there.
No one but Vegeta and Trunks
can still defend themselves.
Not even your father!
He, too, will die.
[CELL JR. 5 &amp; TIEN grunt]
[CELL JR. 6] Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty!
[BOTH grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[CELL JR. 1 growls]
[VEGETA grunts]
[thinking] This is
absolute madness!
They're nothing but children!
Monster!
[CELL JR. 4 grunts]
[CELL JR. 4 giggles,
YAMCHA grunts]
[CELL JR. 4 yells]
[YAMCHA gasps]
[YAMCHA screams]
[GOHAN gasps]
--[CELL JR. 2 squeals]
--[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU grunts]
You guys... I'm sorry...
I... just didn't think...
it could end up this way...
[GOHAN whimpers]
[thinking] Why did
you do this, Dad?!
Why did you count on me so much?
If you're so sure
I have all this power,
then tell me
how to bring it out!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[thinking] I wanna help!
[thinking] I wanna save
you, Dad, but I-I can't!
I don't know how. I'm too
afraid to do this alone!
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
They're plain horrid!
Today's been weird!
[TIEN grunts]
[YAMCHA groans]
[GOKU grunts]
--[CELL JR. 6] Fifty!
--[KRILLIN screams]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[VEGETA yells]
I'll spend no more time playing
with petty creatures like you!
Understand?!
[CELL JR. 1 giggles]
Now disappear!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] Final Flash!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[GOKU gasps]
[CELL JR. 6] Hmm?
[CELL JR. 1 yells]
[CELL JR. 1 giggles]
[VEGETA gasps]
[grunting]
[CELL JR. 6 giggles]
[CELL JR. 1 yells]
[VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU grunting]
[CELL JR. 2 giggles]
[VEGETA yells]
[CELL JR. 1 screams]
[VEGETA &amp; CELL JR. 1 grunt]
Those little freaks
just don't play fair!
You know, we can't keep filming,
when we're torn
into little pieces!
Yes, good point.
What do ya say
we get on out of here?
Our fans'll understand!
Maestro Satan,
can we go with them?
[MR. SATAN] Go if you want!
But a true champion
never runs from danger!
So, you're going to stay here?
You bet!
First I'll go to the hospital
to fix my stomach, of course,
but then I'll return!
[ALL gasp]
Now, I'm off to the doctor
so I can come back and win!
[ANDROID 16] Wait.
[MR. SATAN] Was that you?
[ALL] Mm-mmm.
Huh...?
[ANDROID 16] Wait...
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Please help me.
[ALL scream]
Before you go, please
take me to the area
where the rest
of them are fighting.
That head is talking!
[whimpering]
Please, it is...
for the good of the Earth...
You must be insane!
Cell and all his little
minions are out there!
Yeah, that's right!
We can't let our champ go out
into such a dangerous mess!
I thought you would
be eager to help the planet.
You are its greatest
champion, are you not?
Mr. Satan is the World
Champion of mankind
and that doesn't include
monsters like you and Cell!
You got it?!
Hey, shut up!
They might be monsters but I can
crush them all with one hand!
I just need a doctor first!
Help me, Champion.
[MR. SATAN growls]
[PIIZA] Hercule! Don't listen
to that thing! He's heartless!
[PIROZHKI] And he
has not a body!
[CARONI] Yes!
That's what happens
when you get too close to Cell!
[MR. SATAN growls]
Mr. Satan!
[MR. SATAN] Enough!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
I... will help you.
[gasping]
[ANNOUNCER] You have
to stop! You'll get killed!
Leave me alone!
All these nobodies out there
and even now a kid
is fighting Cell!
[MR. SATAN] It would be shameful
of a world champion to run away!
Please don't go!
Will it be okay if I just
take you somewhere close?
Yes, thank you.
[PICCOLO] Rapid Fire!
[CELL JR. 7 growls]
[MR. SATAN screams]
[MR. SATAN] I can't do this!
It's terrifying!
[ANDROID 16] You are doing fine.
Just throw me from here.
[GOKU grunting]
[CELL JR. 6 yells,
KRILLIN grunts]
No more!
[CELL JR. 4 grunting]
[YAMCHA screams]
[TIEN grunts]
I'm telling you not to do this!
[thinking] Hmph! Just a
little more until he pops!
I can certainly manage that!
[CELL] Playtime is over,
children! You can kill them now!
NOOOO!!!!
[GOHAN growls]
[thinking] Good! Good!
One more push is all he needs!
Hey! Hurry up, now!
First one with
a kill wins a prize!
[MR. SATAN growls]
What?!
[GOHAN] Android... 16...
Oh, that's bad!
I threw him too far!
Gohan, let it go.
It is not a sin to fight
for the right cause.
There are those who
words alone will not reach.
Cell is such a being.
I know how you feel,
Gohan. You are gentle.
You do not like to hurt.
I know because I too
have learned these feelings.
But it is because you cherish
life that you must protect it.
Uegh!
This sentimental
downpour is killing me!
It's so nice of
you to help, 16.
But I plan on doing this my way.
Please, drop your restraints.
Protect the life I loved.
You have the strength.
My scanners sensed it.
Just let it go.
[GOHAN gasps]
[circuit buzzes]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Yet another fighter
you could have saved!
[thinking] 16, you loved
life.
You gave everything
up to save it.
And you were just an
android... I let you die!
I can't do that...
I won't watch any more!
I-I feel it slipping!
[GOHAN thinking] And I
won't watch this anymore!
[GOKU screams]
[screaming continues]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasping]
Gohan...!
[NARRATOR] It is a secret
we have known before
Gohan could even
form words in his mouth.
Through fights with Raditz,
Garlic Jr., the Ginyu Force,
and even Frieza,
we've caught glimpses of
the child's explosive power.
But like an explosion,
it always vanished
with the moment.
It couldn't be
controlled, until now.
At last, the beastly
power has been harnessed.
Gohan has awoken.
Now Cell will battle a warrior
eleven years in the making.
On the next Dragon Ball Z!