[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragonball Z,
things were looking up!
With Piccolo
keeping Frieza busy,
Goku was able to complete
his ultimate weapon,
the Spirit Bomb!
Drawing energy from
all living things,
it was an attack not
even Frieza could ignore!
[FRIEZA] No, that's...
impossible!
[NARRATOR] The awesome power of
the Spirit Bomb seemed too much
for him to handle as he
struggled to hold it back.
[NARRATOR] It was a tense
moment indeed on Planet Namek,
as the hopes of our heroes
were riding on this one attack.
[NARRATOR] Has Goku
finally conquered
the vicious tyrant of space?
[NARRATOR] Will the
universe once again be safe
from Frieza's greedy claws?
[NARRATOR] Stay tuned
to find out today.
You-You think that's
the end of Frieza?
I hope so...
But where's my daddy...?
He was pretty close to
the blast when it went off!
So maybe he...
Maybe he was too close!
Hey, don't worry!
But I can't feel his...
his presence...
That's because you're
not concentrating
hard enough on it, Gohan.
And besides,
he was with Piccolo.
They're both alright.
Hm?
Look...
What is that...?
Over there!
Huh...?
It's Piccolo!
[PICCOLO groans]
Goku!
It's my dad! He's alive!
Yeah-ha-ha!
[BOTH laugh]
Well, Gohan, what're
you waiting for?!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN shouting]
Ah, man...
It's hard to fly
because we used up
most our energy
against Frieza!
Piccolo!
Dad!
[GOHAN] Dad! Piccolo!
Huh...?
[BOTH laughing]
[GOHAN] Dad!
[GOHAN laughs]
Go... han...
Oh, Goku!
Are you... okay?
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOHAN laughs]
Hey, Piccolo...
Yes?
Aw, nothin'...
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOKU chuckles]
Hey...
Sorry to make you worry!
Aww...
Goku, your Spirit Bomb
was just awesome!
It was so huge!
That's because it was
filled with the energy
of every living creature
in the solar system.
I gotta admit, I thought that
I'd never see you again!
Surely you must
have had more faith
in your father than that?
I guess now we can all
get back down to Earth!
For a while there, I
didn't think we'd get back!
Huh?
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
What I meant was, it's not
that I didn't have faith
in Goku it's just...
I'm homesick...
Huh...?
Huh?
Uhh...
[ALL laugh]
Goku has done it!
He's finally defeated Frieza!
[KING KAI laughs]
Oh, happy day!
Happy day!
Woo-hoo!
What are you talking
about, you old kook?!
No one could defeat Frieza!
Impossible...
No way!
You sure?
[GINYU FORCE gasps]
If Goku's won,
then so have we!
And that means if
Piccolo's alive,
then we can get
ourselves back to Earth!
Let's do it!
[yelling]
Attack!
Huh...?
[RECOOM growls]
[YAMCHA laughs]
[JEICE yells]
[BURTER yells]
[TIEN chuckles]
Now you've done it...
Purple Comet Attack!
Comet Flash Attack!
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN yells]
[BURTER &amp; JEICE scream]
Wha-What was that?!
--[BURTER groans]
--[JEICE] Ugh... Ew...
[BOTH yell]
[YAMCHA shouts]
[RECOOME grunts]
And he's down
for the count.
[RECOOME screams]
Ohh, I hate it when
they start to belly flop!
[ALL screaming]
Jeice...?
Burter?
Recoome--?
[GULDO screams]
Hurray! We won!
We won!
We defeated the Ginyu Force!
[RECOOME growls]
Those rats!
Just wait till I
get out of here!
If you think
you're leaving,
you've got another
thing coming,
because it's not so easy
to get out of this place.
We'll see about that!
[RECOOME laughs]
[RECOOME grunts]
[ALL grunt]
[GULDO screams]
[ALL scream]
Way to go, boys!
Your training paid
off handsomely!
You even surprised me with
some of your techniques!
When I invited the
Ginyu Force here,
I never thought
you'd beat them!
You invited those guys?!
Uhhh...!
What I meant to say was that
the Ginyu Force showing up here
was as much of a
surprise for me, too!
I mean, it's not like
I brought them here
to help train
you or anything!
What a silly thought...
So why don't we just forget
about them, shall we?
Good job, men, good job!
You know, I'll bet
you three are glad
I didn't invite Frieza
himself here, aren't you?
Get it? It's a joke!
[KING KAI laughs]
[GOHAN laughs]
Well, guys,
If we leave right now,
it'll take us just about
five days to get home.
Yay! I can see
my mom again!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] And I'll
see all my friends!
[GOHAN laughs]
[KRILLIN screams]
We forgot about Bulma!
What are we going to do?
Don't scare me
like that, Krillin!
For a second I thought
you saw Frieza again!
In some ways, Bulma
is worse than Frieza.
At least that's
the way I feel...
[GOHAN laughs]
[ALL laugh]
[GOKU groans]
Don't make me laugh,
Krillin, I still ache all over.
Well, it looks like
we were too late
to save the Planet Namek.
I just hope Guru and
all of his loyal followers
who were destroyed
can now rest in peace.
W-what?
How in the world do you
know about Guru, Piccolo?
Hmm...?
[KRILLIN gasps]
What is it, Krillin?
[KRILLIN wails]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[PICCOLO growls]
[FRIEZA growls]
[ALL]
It's Frieza!
Th-That's impossible!
You made a direct hit
with your Spirit Bomb
and no one could
survive that!
[GOHAN] Ah... Mommy!
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU gasps]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[PICCOLO] Goku!
[GOKU] Oh, no!
[BOTH gasp]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOHAN whimpers]
No... no...
Piccolo...
No...
Piccollooooooo!
[KING KAI gasps]
No...
How c-could he?
Hey, King Kai.
What is it?
Poor Piccolo...
Poor, poor Piccolo!
[gasping]
But I thought you said that
Goku defeated Frieza?!
[KING KAI] It's all my fault...
I was foolish to think
Frieza could be defeated...
And he's more horrible
than I ever imagined!
[GOHAN whimpers]
Piccolo...?
Hey... Piccolo!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Frie.... za!
[FRIEZA] I must admit that
Spirit Bomb of yours
sure packs a whallop.
It even knocked the
breath out of me.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Gohan! Krillin!
Listen up!
Huh...?
[GOKU] The spaceship I used
to get to this planet
shouldn't be too far from here.
Find Bulma and the ship,
and then get as far away
from here as you can.
Come on!
What are you waiting for?!
[GOHAN gasps]
I'm not going!
I'd never let you
fight Frieza alone!
Listen, Gohan!
You have to get
out of here now!
You don't have a
say in the matter!
But, Goku...
We can't leave...
If you think that your
little friends can escape me,
you're sadly mistaken!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Krillin! Look out!
This time you
won't come back!
Krillin, no!
[KRILLIN screams]
Krillin!
[FRIEZA laughs]
Frieza, stop this!
[FRIEZA growls]
Help me! Ahh--
[gasping]
[KING KAI gasps]
Now who was it?
It was... Krillin...
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
♪ Pop goes the weasel! ♪
I...
won't... let you...
get away with... this...
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOKU snarls]
[GOKU growls]
I won't...
let you...
[GOKU growls]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU screams]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Gohan.
Listen very carefully.
You must leave
this planet now
and take Piccolo
with you, got it?
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU growls]
This is the last time
I'm going to tell you!
Get out of here
right now, Gohan!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GINYU] Ribbit...
Ribbit... Ribbit.
--Ribbit-ribbit.
--[BULMA] Huh...?
Hmm...?
[BULMA gasps]
[NARRATOR] Has Frieza pushed
Goku's rage to new heights?
And can Goku avenge the life
of his close friend Krillin?
The only way to find
out is to watch
the next exciting episode of...
Dragon Ball Z!