[MAN] Please, stay away from us.
We didn't do anything!
[WARRIOR 1]
We never said you did.
[slashing,
screaming]
[laughing]
[GARLIC JR.] Ah, in the
darkness they have taken wing,
never to return again...
[thunder cracks]
[GARLIC JR.] Maybe these poor
fools know how I felt now.
When I was cast off
against my will into
a place from which
there was no escape.
[GARLIC JR.] Into the darkness.
Alone, in a frozen hell
without any light for years.
So many years...
Well I've come back to share.
To share the pain and
the horror that I felt
with every living
thing on Earth.
After ten years of exile
in the Dead Zone,
I, Garlic Jr., have
returned to Earth
to hatch a sinister plan of
destruction and revenge.
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Come on!
Catch me if you can!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] C'mon, faster!
[SABERTOOTH TIGER yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
Wow.
[KRILLIN] Hey, yo.
Hey, Krillin.
Wow. Is that really
you under there?
Yeah, sweetheart. See?
That's the worst
Humphrey Bogart imitation
I've ever heard.
So whatcha been doing, partner?!
Ehh, not much.
[KRILLIN screams]
[GOHAN] It looks like we'll
be having fish for a while.
Hey, do you want to help
me gut and clean 'em?
Uh, no thanks.
Hey, come on.
Hey!
[GOHAN] Let's go for
a swim, then.
The water is ice-cold.
It feels really incredible.
No, please, no.
Huh?
Sorry. It's the threads, bro.
Ahh. Well, no big deal.
Take 'em off.
[KRILLIN] Uh, well, uhh...
Huh?
Oh, wow. Check out that car!
Is it yours?! For real?!
Yep. Well, uh, sort of.
Aw, what the heck.
It's been so long.
One little dip
won't hurt anything.
Ha-ha!
Last one in is a rotten egg.
[WOMAN] Krillin! Hey!
What are you doing?!
Are you coming, or what?
Yeah, sure! One sec!
Who is she? What's up?
Hmph!
[KRILLIN] She's my,
uh, well, she's uh...
[WOMAN] Krillin. You didn't
forget about me, did you?
Who me?
Yeah, you. Who's that?
Oh, this is my martial
arts partner, Gohan.
Gohan this is
my "friend", Maron.
Hi.
Is he from outer-space?
No, Maron, this isn't the one.
It's his dad, remember?
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
Well, he sure is cute,
though. Did you know that?
Well, sort of.
[MARON giggles]
[MARON] Modest, huh?
And look at this
beautiful black hair.
I know a lot of girls
that would kill
to have hair like this.
[MARON] Do you always hang
out in your underwear?
[MARON giggles]
How cute.
[KRILLIN yells]
Hey, easy! What's the deal?!
What's the deal with you?
You're not jealous, are you?
I thought he was your friend.
[KRILLIN stammers]
Yeah, well, he is.
You're so silly. Here.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[MARON giggles]
Oh. Uh... Hah...
Hey, Gohan, guess what?
What?
There's a party, bro.
Later on this afternoon
at Master Roshi's place.
Think you can make it?
Yeah, sure.
Well, that is, if my
mom'll let me go.
Oh, yeah. She's too darn strict
with all of that studying.
[GOHAN groans]
Oh, well. Maybe a
miracle will happen
and she'll say yes.
Stranger things have
happened, you know.
Yeah...
Ciao!
Laters.
[thinking] I wonder if she's...?
Bye!
[MARON giggles]
Yeah, she is! She's
Krillin's girlfriend!
He did it!
After all these years,
he finally found a girlfriend.
Boy, is Dad gonna be
surprised when he gets back.
[blows landing,
PICCOLO grunts]
[grunting continues]
[blows landing]
[PICCOLO yells]
[KAMI] Thank goodness.
I was beginning to think
I needed glasses.
What? You. And what
are you doing here?
Thanks. Nice welcome.
Same Piccolo.
You're still rude, arrogant,
and completely lacking
in social graces.
But this is just the exterior;
the hard, protective,
outer-shell.
Inside, you've
changed a great deal,
which is why I have come
here to talk to you.
I was hoping that you
would ascend to the throne
and take over my position
as guardian of the Earth.
What...?
[PICCOLO yells]
I'm not interested
in your stinking job.
But... I have been a
little worried about you.
Huh?
[PICCOLO] I've seen
some disturbing
images in my meditation
lately, and, I'm not sure,
but I think they're
glimpses of the future.
There might be some
trouble brewing
so... just be careful,
that's all.
Piccolo...
[MR. POPO hums]
Huh?
Oh no...
[laughing]
[WARRIOR 2] Yoo-hoo.
[grunting]
[GARLIC JR.] Enough.
I said enough!
[MR. POPO gasps]
It's you. Garlic Jr.!
Very observant, Mr. Popo.
[MR. POPO] What do you want?
[GARLIC JR. snickers]
[snickering continues]
Yes, sure, I remember
it all clearly now.
Why you came before.
Now, Dragon! Arise!
[MR. POPO] You were
going to use
the legion of dark
spirits upon the Earth.
So first, you stole
the Dragon Balls
and used them to
wish for immortality.
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
Huh...?
[GARLIC JR. screams]
[MR. POPO] Kami tried to
stop you, but he's getting old
and he's not as spry
as he used to be.
[MR. POPO] Try as he might,
he wasn't able to stop you,
and you finally overpowered him.
[KAMI yells]
[GARLIC JR. shouts]
[KAMI grunts]
[MR. POPO] It was an
easy victory for you,
but when Goku and
Piccolo intervened,
you were forced to transform
and use your maximum power
to finally overcome them.
[MR. POPO] But there was one
thing you hadn't counted on:
Goku's son.
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN] Don't you hurt my
Daddy! Leave him alone!
[MR. POPO] Even though
he was just a boy,
he had phenomenal powers.
[GARLIC JR. growls]
You pest! How are
you doing this?!
[GOHAN growls]
[GARLIC JR. shouts]
[GOHAN grunts]
Into the void you go!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[MR. POPO] He didn't
care about himself,
it was his love for his father
that awakened his
sleeping powers.
He couldn't stand
to see his father
sucked into the
horrible Dead Zone Vortex
that you created.
[GOHAN growls]
[MR. POPO] So he
exploded with rage
and his fantastic power bounced
you into that horrible prison
that you intended for others.
We thought you
were gone forever.
[GARLIC JR. yells]
[GARLIC JR.] Don't look so
disappointed, Mr. Popo.
Kami's getting
close to retirement.
He's going to need
a competent successor.
Whatd'ya think, Mr. Popo?
Do I fit the bill?
Am I not the ideal
candidate to be
the next guardian
of the Earth?
Please. Well? Tell me, Mr. Pop.
You can be honest.
Speak your mind.
Well, what's the matter?!
Tongue tied?! Rogue.
You don't think I'd be
good for the job, do you?!
[WARRIORS laugh]
[MR. POPO] Magic Carpet!
[GARLIC JR.] Get him!
--Right, Boss!
[WARRIOR 3 yells]
[MR. POPO gasps]
I... can't budge...
[WARRIORS laugh]
[GARLIC JR.] Yes, this
is a very special net.
It paralyzes those
captured in it.
Ease up, boys.
[GARLIC JR.] Now, Popo.
Where is Kami?
[MR. POPO] I don't know.
[GARLIC JR.] You're lying!
No! Mr. Popo does not lie!
For some reason I believe you.
Yes, that's because I don't lie!
Bah. You disgust me!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[MR. POPO gasps]
Pint-sized Popo. Don't
bother trying to escape.
That tiny, little energy
field is impregnable.
[GARLIC JR.] Ahh, there you are.
You look so scared.
Don't worry, I'm not going
to kill you yet, Mr. Popo.
All in due time.
All in due time!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
What a day. This is great!
All of us here together!
Really. Hey,
speaking of together,
are you guys officially dating?
Uh-huh! Well, sort of. We're
not boyfriend and girlfriend.
Huh? Oh, so we're still
free to date other people?
Well, then, what d'ya
say we go out?
Uh? Yeah. Yeah, sure. Why not?
[YAMCHA yells]
Say what?!
My goodness!
Come on, Bulma.
We were joking. Right?
Tell her, Maron.
No, I'm serious.
Oh, no..
[BULMA] Enough kidding around!
Maron you haven't said
much about Krillin.
What's makes him
so special to you?
Gosh, that's a good one...
Uhh...
Well, he's bald!
♪ Oh. Love is in the air. ♪
♪ And it's gonna
crash and burn. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah. ♪
Bald is beautiful.
[ROSHI] Hmm...
Something needs to be
done about this...
[ROSHI chuckles]
--[BULMA laughs]
--[ROSHI] Krillin!
We need to talk, son.
Why so serious? What's the deal?
[ROSHI] Krillin, I'm your
Master and teacher
and you know full well
that you're not allowed
to have a girlfriend unless
I approve of her first.
Yeah, but it all
happened so fast.
Forget about that stupid code!
Master. Come on!
Cut him some slack!
Sorry, I can't. I have to
do what's best for Krillin!
Sure, no prob. So I have to
pass some sort of test, huh?
I'm positive that I can
win your approval, sir!
Good. I'm glad. Maybe you can.
[ROSHI coughs]
And here's what
I want you to do...
What is it?
Spill it.
Yeah, tell me!
Just give me a
little kiss, baby!
Right here! Right on the kisser!
[ROSHI squeals]
You dirty old man!
Go away.
Joke. I'm... joking!
[laughing]
[GOHAN] Please, Mom?
[CHICHI] No, Gohan.
I already told you. No.
But why...?
[CHICHI] Because you need
to study, that's why.
Mmm, that's not bad...
Mom, just this once.
Gohan, you know how
important your studies are.
You don't want to fail
and blow your chances
of getting into college
someday, do you?
No...
Then be a good boy
and do as I say.
Now this conversation is over.
[GOHAN groans]
Poor boy. It's so hard.
Hm? What's this?
What happened here?!
[KAMI] Come out, whoever
you are! I see you...
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
[KAMI] What?! Garlic, Jr.!
Impossible!
[GARLIC JR.] Don't have a
heart attack, old man.
I don't want you
to die before I have
the pleasure of killing you!
[KAMI] You're even more
arrogant than before.
Only a brat like
you would destroy
a beautiful sanctuary like this!
[GARLIC JR.] What business
is it of yours, Kami?
This is my sanctuary now.
[KAMI] Mr. Popo. Can you
hear me. Mr. Popo?
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
This what you want?
[MR. POPO] Sorry, Kami!
[GARLIC JR.] As new
guardian of the Earth,
the first change I'm making
is to hire a groundskeeper
who's actually tall enough
to water the plants.
Why, you fiend! You'll
never get away with this!
Your dark plans have no
firm foundation to stand on!
They're going to crumble.
You can't succeed!
Yes I can.
You were lucky last time.
If it wasn't for that kid,
I'd be sitting on your
throne already.
In your dreams. I'll die
before I let that happen!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
Oh my, I couldn't have
said it any better myself.
I'm taking over,
and you are going to die!
[GARLIC JR. yells]
[KAMI thinking]
He's too fast to detect!
[KAMI shouts]
[blows landing,
KAMI grunts]
[KAMI yells]
--[WARRIORS yell]
--[KAMI] What the...?
[WARRIORS laugh]
Nice. Good work.
We'll keep him alive
for the time being.
That way we can use
the Dragon Balls.
What? Oh, no!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
You are a sight to behold.
You have no idea how much
I'm loving this, old man.
Fool! You won't succeed!
My, my, those are
awfully big words
from such a tiny little man.
You're too much.
Don't you get it, you
feeble, joke of a guardian?
Your time has come.
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[CHICHI hums]
Gosh, I'm sorry,
Mom. Man, I'm bad.
Thanks. Being bad's not easy.
Well, let's blaze.
What d'ya say?
[growls]
Shh.
[GOHAN laughs]
Whoa. Look at that
sunset, Icarus!
[door creaks open]
[GARLIC JR.] Now where would
that green goody-two-shoes
hide my father's
Black Water Mist?
Hmm? Wouldn't you know it.
That dodo left it
right here in the open.
Ah, yes, this is it, all right.
With this, we don't need
an army. We'll make one.
What d'ya mean, Boss?
[GARLIC JR. grunts]
[GARLIC JR.] When people
breath this mist,
any evil tendencies
that they're resisting
take control of
their character.
They become mad with desire for
wealth and material pleasure
to the point of wanting to
kill each other for it.
You see, boys,
our army of darkness
has always been here.
We just have to wake it up.
You're a genius, Lord Garlic.
What a brilliant plan.
Yeah, you've really outdone
yourself this time, Boss.
Why, thank you.
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[NARRATOR] With Kami and
Mr. Popo powerless to stop him,
Garlic Jr. has released
the Black Water Mist
onto the Earth.
As Gohan flies unsuspectingly
to meet his friends,
the evil mist descends.
What darkness does it portend?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!