[NARRATOR] Last
time on Dragon Ball Z...
As the two evil Saiyans
hurtled through space
on their quest to
destroy the Earth,
Gohan was giving
Piccolo a brief preview
of what would happen
upon their arrival!
Gohan underwent
a horrifying change
as he unconsciously discovered
the Saiyans' secret power...
their ability to transform
at the full moon.
And while Goku sought
the Other-Worldly training
he needs to defend his
home against the Saiyans
in one year's time,
Piccolo was busy ensuring he
would have a home to return to.
Powerless to fight
the giant ape head on,
Piccolo put a stop to
Gohan's devastating rampage
the only way
he knew how!
[PICCOLO] That tail gives them
the ability to transform. There!
[NARRATOR] After removing
the possibility of
another monstrous relapse,
Piccolo equipped Gohan with
the tools he would need
to survive his
wilderness training.
And with that,
the mighty green warrior
took his leave to begin some
intense training of his own.
What new trials await our
heroes? Find out today!
[GOHAN] Wow... How did I
get down from that cliff?
I can't remember
anything...
Oh, well.
At least I'm down...
Ahh...
Time for
breakfast!
Oh yeah. I should
wash my face first...
[stammers]
[growls]
Uh, hey, what's going on?
Something...
Something's wrong...
Aaahhh!
My tail is gone!
What happened?
Where'd it go?
What the...
These aren't
my clothes! Huh?
[GOHAN thinking]
This is weird...
Aaaahhhh!
Aahh! Ah!
Stay back! Aahh!
Aahhh!
Get away from me!
Uhh...
Aaahhh!
Stop it! I said
leave me alone!
[growling]
Huh?! Aaahh!
You don't want me
for breakfast!
Wouldn't you rather have a
bowl of cereal or something?
Bad kitty!
[screeching]
[GOHAN]
Hey! What are you doing?
Let go! Put me down!
[GOHAN screams]
[squawks]
Help! Somebody!
Help me please! Help!
[GOKU thinking] I need
to find some food...
What's a guy gotta do to
get a burger around here?
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN] This sure
is a weird place,
and those pictures
on the wall...
They look like...
They look just like something
I saw in my history book.
Aaahh!
Huh?
A-Aaahhh!
[GOHAN]
What is that thing?
And what's it doing way out
here in the middle of nowhere?
Hmm...
[beeping and whirring]
[ROBOT]
Who's there?
Who took me out
of stand-by mode?
Stand-by--Whoa!
It's talking!
[ROBOT] Who are you?
What do you want?
[GOHAN]
I'm, uh...
My name is Gohan, sir!
[ROBOT] Well, Gohan.
Keep your voice down!
What are you trying to do,
bury us under tons of sand?
[GOHAN whispers]
My name is Gohan!
[ROBOT]
I heard you.
[GOHAN] What are you doing
out here in this place?
[ROBOT] That's none
of your business!
Just put me back in stand-by
mode and get out of here!
But there's
no way out...
[ROBOT] Except for that
trail right behind me.
[GOHAN]
What? Uhh!
[GOHAN laughs]
Ah! All right!
[ROBOT] Wait...
[GOHAN] Huh?
[ROBOT]
Stand-by mode?
[GOHAN]
Oh yeah...
[powers down]
Thanks for
everything!
Ha, ha, ha...
Aaahh!
I can't even
see the bottom!
Mr. Robot!
Mr. Robot, I can't...
[ROBOT]
Stop yelling!
Don't you remember
what I told you?
I said I can't make it
down from way up here.
[ROBOT]
That's not my problem.
Uh, but...
[ROBOT] Now put me
back in stand-by mode
and get out of here.
Thanks and have
a nice day!
Nope! Don't
think so...
But I can't get out of here
all by myself! I can't!
[ROBOT]
Stop yelling!
Now cut that out, or
you'll bury us both!
Look, I told you how to get out
of here. What's your problem?
What are you, some
kind of cry-baby?
Don't you realize that if
you don't leave right now,
you might be trapped
here forever?
Now get
out of here!
Did you leave?
Gohan! Come back!
You forgot to put me
back in stand-by mode!
He's gone. Now I'm stuck
here forever, wide awake.
I can already feel my power
cells draining away...
Uh, hello?
[ROBOT] You...
You're still here?
I get it! You can't see.
You're eyes are turned off!
Heh, heh, heh. I'll fix 'em!
[ROBOT]
No, wait! Stop that!
I don't want your help!
Stop... Stop touching that!
What do you think you're doing?
Don't plug that in!
I don't need to see
anything down here.
You're wasting
precious power!
That's better.
[ROBOT]
Why you meddlesome little...
Hey, you really are little...
What's a kid like you
doing way out here
in my neck
of the woods?
This place
is dangerous!
I know and this
cave is so high.
There's no way
I can jump down!
[ROBOT] Well...
You're just going to have to,
if you want to
stay alive, that is.
But you could help me
get out of here, right?
Couldn't you?
[ROBOT] Of course,
but I'm not going to!
[rumbling]
You're going to have to learn
how to take care of yourself.
Now stop
bothering me!
[ROBOT] Now put me back in
stand-by mode and leave...
I've already wasted
too much power
dealing with you
and your problems.
[powers down]
[sobs]
[GOHAN snores]
[snoring]
Mmm! You mean
this is a buffet?
Alright!
All-you-can-eat!
Aaahhhh!
Wake up!
Please, help me!
[ROBOT] What-what?!
What is it this time?
There's a scorpion!
[ROBOT] Well, this is a cave.
Caves have scorpions.
[GOHAN]
But I'm scared...
[ROBOT] They also have snakes,
and bats, and spiders.
Now stop being such a baby
and put me back into stand-by.
[powers down]
[whimpers]
[GOKU thinking] I'm so hungry,
I could eat a, a, a...
Hey, I wonder what
cloud tastes like...
[beeping and whirring]
Me again... Do you
have anything to eat?
[ROBOT] Oh, yes!
Being a robot, I always
keep plenty of food
just lying around.
What do you think?
Hungry...
[ROBOT] You could
always make yourself
a nice snake and
scorpion sandwich...
[GOHAN sobs]
[ROBOT]
Now, for the last time,
put me back in stand-by mode
and stop bothering me!
[GOHAN sobs]
[ROBOT]
Keep it down!
But I'm starving!
[GOHAN cries loudly]
[ROBOT] Look, if you just
stop crying, I'll help you.
But you've got to learn
to control yourself, alright?
[GOHAN] Mm-hm.
[ROBOT] At this time of year,
the sun shines through a hole
in the far right
corner of the cave.
If you go there and
look very carefully,
you might find
some vegetation.
That way.
[GOHAN laughs]
Whew!
That was great!
Ahh!
[GOHAN] Look what I found!
Right where you said they'd be!
[ROBOT] Great!
Glad to have helped.
Well, I guess it's time
for stand-by mode again.
But... I can't
eat these raw.
[ROBOT] You're never
going to survive out here
with that kind
of attitude.
Hey, wait... Aren't you
a Capsule Corp. robot?
Yeah, I recognize some
of your markings, now.
If you're a Capsule
Corp. robot,
that means you should
have some sort of
built-in cooking system.
Capsule Corp. robots are
supposed to be the best robots
in the whole world!
[ROBOT] Well, I, uh...
I suppose that is true.
Hey! Let's see how that
cooking system works!
[GOHAN] Right!
[ROBOT] How would you
like them prepared?
[GOHAN]
Steamed, please.
[ROBOT]
You've got it!
[GOHAN giggles]
[ROBOT] Would you
like any seasoning?
Something spicy or mild?
[GOHAN] Hmm... Can you make them
the same way that my mom does?
[ROBOT]
Uh, well, I, uh... [ding]
Oh, look.
They're done!
[GOHAN]
Ahh...
These sure
taste weird...
[ROBOT] You're welcome.
Hey, wait a minute!
Well, if you don't
like it, then I guess--
It's good.
I'm sorry!
It's just not mom's...
I miss her so much
and I have no idea
where I am or how
to get back home.
[ROBOT] Yes, that
must be difficult...
And traveling through
this endless desert
to get back there seems
nearly impossible.
Yeah...
[ROBOT] Even if
you knew the way,
everything else is
still against you...
The sun, the wind,
no food or water...
Mr. Robot...
Why are you here?
[ROBOT]
An accident...
Accident?
[ROBOT] I was here to
excavate these ruins.
While I was examining
the ancient hieroglyphics,
there was an
earthquake...
The walls of this
cave were unstable,
and they collapsed
all around me...
I've been stuck down
here ever since.
Wait! Now I remember!
The pictures on the wall!
[ROBOT] What are
you talking about?
They were in my
history book!
That means that the next
time someone comes here
to study them,
they can rescue us!
[ROBOT] But, you're the first
person I've seen in 30 years.
Hey! What are you
doing? Answer me!
[GOHAN] I'm going to
get you out of here!
[ROBOT] Stop that!
I don't need your help...
I'll leave
when I'm ready!
Haven't you heard a word
I've said? Stop digging!
You're almost free, then
we can leave here together!
[ROBOT] I'm storing
up my energy...
Then I can jump out of here on
my own without anyone's help!
Wait! You're
causing a cave-in!
Aaahhhh!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[ROBOT] Get out of here!
I can't hold this thing forever!
Huh? But you're...
[ROBOT] You must leave now!
Use the path I showed you!
[GOHAN] I can't leave
you here! I can't!
[ROBOT]
You have to!
If you don't, you'll
be buried here forever.
Get moving! I can
take care of myself!
Gohan, please!
This is your last chance.
Climb over me to the pathway
and leave this place! Quickly!
Alright...
[ROBOT] Now jump!
Jump out as far as you can!
What are you waiting for?
Do it! Now!
Right!
[rumbling]
I... can't do it!
[ROBOT] Have you
lost your mind?
[hissing]
[GOHAN screams]
[ROBOT]
Gohan...
I stopped this pillar
from crushing us...
But now you are cut off
from the only way out...
Now listen to me
very carefully...
Reach inside my head
and connect the blue
wire to the red one.
They are
right up front.
[GOHAN]
Connect the...
--[ROBOT] Quickly!
--[GOHAN] Right!
[ROBOT] This will route
all of my reserve energy
into my power cells...
Hurry! This place
is coming down fast!
Got it!
[ROBOT grunts]
[ROBOT]
Full Power!
[grunting continues]
[GOHAN quivers]
[ROBOT]
Ready, Gohan?
Ready for what?
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN]
Mr. Robot!
Mr. Robot?
Aahh!
Mr. Robot!
It's my fault.
All my fault...
I'm so sorry...
[ROBOT]
Gohan?
I'm here! I thought
you'd left me.
[ROBOT] Not just yet,
but soon...
Throwing that pillar
drained all of the energy
in my power cells.
Even my reserves...
[ROBOT] Come now, Gohan...
That won't do any good.
[GOHAN]
Don't go...
[ROBOT] Remember what
I told you, Gohan.
You have to learn to take care
of yourself. Be strong...
[GOHAN sobs]
[GOHAN]
Please!
[ROBOT] No more
stand-by mode.
It's time to shut down...
[voice deepens]
Time to shut down.
Uh?! Mr. Robot?
Wake up!
Come on! Wake up!
Please don't leave me!
Let me help you, the
same way you helped me!
You can't go!
Please! Mr. Robot!
[sobs]
[GOHAN thinks] I don't
know if I can make it
on my own out here...
But I'll try...
I will try...
[NARRATOR] What awaits
young Gohan as he continues
his life-changing
training?
And what will
Goku find
down this long and winding
path in the clouds?
With every moment they
spend finding out,
the Saiyans move a
moment closer to Earth.
The story continues next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!