[GOHAN cheers]
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
it seemed like a time
for celebration.
Old friends
rejoiced together.
[KRILLIN] Are you okay?
[GOHAN] Piccolo...
[NARRATOR] And new
friends were reunited.
[NARRATOR] However, the
nightmare wasn't over yet.
And Frieza renewed his attack
on the battle-weary Goku!
[NARRATOR] But an
incredible sacrifice from
the lion-hearted Piccolo saved
Goku from certain destruction.
[NARRATOR] Few men have the
courage for such a noble act.
Piccolo had truly transformed
into a being of greatness.
This time, you won't come back!
[NARRATOR] The next man
on Frieza's hit list:
Goku's best friend, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Help me! Ahh--
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR] It was
a tough day indeed
for the virtuous warriors
from planet Earth...
Beaten, battered,
but not defeated,
the loss of his friends
and their radical acts
of unselfishness caused a
transformation in Goku
that he had never
experienced before!
Goha, listen very carefully.
You must leave this planet now
and take Piccolo with you.
Got it?
Just do as I say, Gohan!
Leave me now!
Can't you see?!
I need to be alone!
Uh, right!
[NARRATOR] What does this
golden transformation mean?
Has the legendary Super
Saiyan emerged at last?
Find out, today!
What... What now?!
Saiyans transform into apes!
This is completely
different from anything
that I've ever seen before!
Darn!
What does this mean?!
Gohan!
It's time!
Piccolo is our only chance
of bringing the others
back to this dimension!
Take him to the ship and go!
But what about you?
Don't worry about me now!
I know that I'm
where I need to be!
But... if we take the ship,
that means you'll be stranded
out here with no way home!
I'm your father, now listen!
Gohan, just do as I say!
Whatever you want, Dad.
[GOHAN] C'mon, Piccolo.
[GOHAN] It's time for
us to get out of here.
I love you, Dad...
Goku, my Dad!
I understand.
What Vegeta said
came true after all!
The legend!
My father,
a Super Saiyan!
[FRIEZA laughs]
Amusingly
vivid imagination.
Only I decide who
leaves here today.
Hmph.
Huh?!
Wha--?!
[FRIEZA grunts]
Ow!
[FRIEZA growls]
You just don't
know when to stop.
Enough is enough!
[FRIEZA screams]
First, Vegeta,
then Piccolo,
and now, my best
friend, Krillin!
[FRIEZA growls]
You don't care!
I can see that!
Their lives mean
absolutely nothing to you!
You're not in the
least bit sorry!
Even now, all you can think
about is how to destroy me!
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA grunting]
How?! How did you get
this incredible power?!
Don't tell me...
I-It's true!
Isn't it?!
How wild!
It just happened!
He just changed!
It was like he was on fire!
That's my Dad..
He's so great!
Wow, and I'm his son!
[hammer clanking]
[DR. BRIEF] Well,
what d'ya think?
Could this be it, Scratch?
[SCRATCH meows]
[DR. BRIEF] Hm! It
looks like you're right!
But we're running out of
options, my furry friend...
Hey!
What the heck's
going on up there?!
[DR. BRIEF] We're still trying
to isolate the problem, ChiChi!
How complicated
could it be?!
If I have to come
up there, I will!
[thinking] Doesn't this come
with an owner's manual
or something?
[DR. BRIEF] Hey, cut us a
little slack down there!
Nobody can trouble-shoot
a frozen osiphilator
like we can!
[CHICHI] What do you mean
"we", you're by yourself!
[SCRATCH yowls]
[CHICHI] Oh, so we're relying on
a cat to get us into deep space!
[DR. BRIEF] This
isn't an ordinary cat!
She's had four years experience!
Hey, what's up?
You look worried.
What's the deal?
[ROSHI] Mmm!
[CHICHI] I don't care if you
won the Nobel Peace Prize!
You're a kook!
And so is your cat!
Strange! This life!
It's always full of
unexpected twists and turns!
[YAJIROBE] So what's up?
It's Goku!
Something's happened
to Goku, I can feel it!
I've had a sixth sense about
Goku since he was a boy.
Is he dead?
Oh, no, that's not it!
He kept digging and he
finally hit the mother lode!
A power so great that normal
men can't even fathom it!
So what?
Isn't that good?
[ROSHI] Not necessarily.
Having the kind of power
that I'm talking about is
uncharted territory for Goku.
He's never experienced
anything like it.
That much
I can guarantee!
Yes, sir!
A power of this
magnitude could overwhelm
a man and change
him forever!
[YAJIROBE] Say what?!
Right now, Goku's
struggling to hold on
to who he is!
God bless him.
Yep, shoot!
All we can do is pray.
[hammer clanging]
No more!
No more...
[FRIEZA gasps]
[GOKU growls]
Now you will
know the horror,
Friezaaa!
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[GOKU shouts]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA roars]
Why do you loathe
what I've done so much?
Saiyans are just as
ruthless as I am.
They were killers,
all of them.
And you have the gaul to
condemn what I've done?
You and your bloodthirsty race!
They paid for
their mistakes!
[FRIEZA giggles]
Is that why they died?
I thought it was
because I killed them.
You're just a beast!
With no conscience!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] So I'm a beast, huh?
Oh, and what about you,
Mr. Super Saiyan?
Aren't you just like me?
Hmph.
So, the jury's still
out on that one.
Let's just give it
a little more time!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA shouts]
Huh...?
Oh, man, Dad!
No... Don't look...
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA yells]
[thinking] Don't
look back, Gohan!
Whatever you do,
don't look back!
Your evil deeds are like
a noose around your neck!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA growls]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[grunting continues]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
What?! But how?!
How could he dodge
it at this range?!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA shouts]
It can't be...
Hey! Why can't I hit you?!
Just tell me!
You didn't say "please."
"Please"...?
What?! "Please"?!
[FRIEZA growls]
You-- Alright then...
Please!
Huh?!
[FRIEZA gasps]
You can destroy planets,
but you can never destroy
what I am, "friend".
Y-You!
What... What are you?!
I am the hope
of the Universe.
I am the answer to all living
things that cry out for peace.
I am protector
of the innocent.
I am the light in the darkness.
I am truth!
Ally to good!
Nightmare to you!
[NARRATOR] How will Frieza
be able to stand up to Goku
now that the legendary
power of the Super Saiyan
has awakened within him?
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!