[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
a menacing force is
rapidly approaching.
[FRIEZA] There it is...
Planet Earth, dead ahead.
[GOHAN]
I feel it too! This isn't good!
[NARRATOR] A force that
greatly concerned Gohan.
[GOHAN] But who is it?
Dad, where are you?
[NARRATOR] The power seemed
to be felt by everyone on Earth.
[YAMCHA] Wait! How do you know?
I know! I make it my
business to know! Unlike you!
There's two of them, Chiaotzu!
My gosh! I've never
felt anything like it!
Tien, I'm scared!
[NARRATOR] Even King Kai
sensed the malevolent prescence.
[KING KAI] I know, Bubbles,
yes! I can feel it too...
[NARRATOR] It's time for
our heroes to get ready,
because this danger is
worse than they think.
[CHICHI]
Oh no! Dad!
[GOHAN growls]
[NARRATOR]
Frieza's back!
And he's got his evil
eye set on Earth.
[GOHAN growls]
This can't be happening!
[GOHAN] If Frieza's
really on his way here,
then we're gonna need
all the help we can get!
Come on, Krillin.
Where are you?!
[KRILLIN]
Hey!
[GOHAN] Krillin!
A-Are you sure it's Frieza?
Are you sure it couldn't
be someone else?
No, Gohan, I can smell him!
I'll never forget that stench!
If you think that your
little friends can escape me,
you're sadly mistaken!
Krillin! Look out!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN wails]
This time you won't come back!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[KRILLIN yelling]
Help me! Ah--!
[GOHAN]
I just can't figure it out!
I thought for sure my
dad finished off Frieza
once and for all!
So did I! But it looks
like we were both
wrong this time, Gohan.
[KING COLD]
Ah, yes!
I've always so enjoyed
the last few quiet moments
before laying a planet to waste.
But I must say, I'm feeling
almost as anxious as you
to reach our
destination, Frieza.
I'm quite curious
to meet this Saiyan!
After all, I've heard
so much about him,
one could hardly blame me.
[FRIEZA growls]
Seems something's got your
blood boiling. Yes, son?
Mm-mmm! We mustn't let our
tempers get the best of us.
[FRIEZA] You've got me
figured all wrong, Father,
I was just admiring the view!
It's simply
electrifying, I'd say!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[YAMCHA] I can't believe
how fast Vegeta is!
I can hardly keep up with him!
[VEGETA thinking]
Perhaps Kakarot wasn't as strong
as I had imagined, after all!
Frieza's still alive!
And I can sense
that his power level
is even greater than before.
But I'll soon show him!
So is mine!
[CHIAOTZU] I don't like this,
Tien! They're coming!
I sense them!
[CHIAOTZU whimpers]
[SPACESHIP CAPTAIN]
We're in final approach
to Earth, your Excellency.
[KING COLD]
Very good.
This is the place where
he'll be touching down!
[YAMCHA]
Are you sure, Vegeta?
Yes, I'm sure! Now zip it!
I don't want him
to know we're waiting!
[YAMCHA growls]
[BULMA]
Hello down there!
[YAMCHA]
It's Bulma!
Vegeta! Yamcha! I'm coming in!
[PUAR giggling]
[PUAR] Yamcha!
[YAMCHA] What in the world
are you two doing here?!
We came to see Frieza!
I missed him on Namek
and I'm not going to
let that happen again!
Are you crazy?! Do you
realize what he'll do to you
when he finds you here?!
Yes, of course I do!
He'll come down
and blow up the planet
but I want to see
him before he does it.
What's so wrong with that?
Besides, I hear he's kinda cute!
[VEGETA] It's amazing how
every time you open your mouth
you prove you're an idiot!
[YAMCHA]
Huh?
Tien! Chiaotzu!
[TIEN] Vegeta! I didn't realize
you were going to be here too!
Is that okay?
[TIEN]
As a matter of fact, it isn't!
I still haven't forgotten what
happened the last time we met!
You disgust me!
How can you stomach him, Yamcha?
Ha! Loser!
What?!
Hey, cool it, guys!
This is no time to fight, okay?
[TIEN growls]
[VEGETA] Hmph.
[YAMCHA sighs]
It's Frieza, isn't it?
How long 'til he lands?
Could be any time now...
Be quiet! I'd rather
Frieza's scouters didn't
detect us because of
your incessant jabbering!
Besides, all this scary talk
is upsetting the Namek.
[YAMCHA]
The Namek?
[ALL gasp]
[YAMCHA]
Piccolo!
How long have you
been standing there?
[PICCOLO] Long enough to hear
all of your senseless bickering!
Look, Gohan! Down there!
[GOHAN] Wow! It looks
like everybody's here!
[KRILLIN] Guess it's safe to say
we came to the right place!
Hey there!
Wow! Gohan! Krillin!
You made it!
Huh? Hey! Any word from Goku?
[BULMA laughing]
[BULMA sighs]
[PUAR sighs]
[YAMCHA]
I just thought I'd ask...
[PICCOLO gasps]
He's here!
[ALL gasping]
[ALL growling, gasping]
[KRILLIN] He's landing
just over that ridge!
[PUAR whimpering]
[BULMA sobbing]
It's... like I dreamed!
Frieza! He's really here!
Gohan, try to focus,
bro. We need you!
[SPACESHIP CAPTAIN] Your
Excellency, the landing process
is complete. We have
reached our destination.
[KING COLD]
Superb!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[ALL gasping]
[ALL gasping, grunting]
Now, there's no
room for mistakes!
We've all got to keep our
power levels suppressed
or else Frieza will pick
us up on his scouters.
Ready?
[YAMCHA]
This is crazy!
I've never felt
anything anywhere close
to the amount of power
I'm sensing right now!
I hate to say it,
Yamcha, but this is only
the tip of the iceberg!
There's no way we're
gonna last very long
against a massive
force like that!
Hey, you guys
are kidding, right?
I-I mean, you're not
suggesting that we attack him?
Like Tien said,
we'd all be wiped out!
I'm telling you,
Frieza's a monster!
And attacking him is suicide!
[PICCOLO]
But we have to try, Yamcha.
Unless we stop Frieza
right here and now,
you may as well kiss the
entire planet goodbye!
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[BOTH sigh]
[TIEN growls]
[VEGETA]
He's right, you know.
You really have no choice.
So what say we put an end
to all of this pathetic
whimpering and go find Frieza!
Before he finds us...
[FRIEZA]
So this is the planet Earth.
My, how very quaint!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA whimpering]
[FRIEZA growling]
[GOKU] It was enough
to beat you, Frieza.
Now, live with the shame. Keep
it bottled up inside, silently.
[FRIEZA grunts]
Poor, stupid Saiyan! You
honestly think you've won?
Your puny mind never
could understand.
I am Frieza, the most
powerful being in the universe!
And you are nothing
but a monkey!
[FRIEZA] You can't win.
Because I am mighty
and you are not.
Now learn!
Learn what happens
when you mess
with the most powerful
being in the universe!
[GOKU]
You fool!
[FRIEZA yelping]
[weakly]
Monkey! He was just a monkey!
[CAPTAIN BLUE] Sire, much as
we expected, the entire planet
Namek has been destroyed
by the explosion.
And, well, uh, all though
there seems to be no signs
of Lord Frieza just
yet, your highness,
we are continuing our
search among the debris
and we're very hopeful that--
Uh...
[KING COLD]
You disappoint me, Captain.
It seems you lack
confidence in Frieza's ability
to survive such a pitiful blast.
I tell you, my son is not so
easily destroyed as a planet.
He is out there, alive!
So, please do go and
find him, won't you?
[KING COLD chuckling]
[CAPTAIN BLUE gasping]
[CAPTAIN BLUE screams]
I've found him, Sire!
It's a very faint signal,
but we have locked on
to Lord Frieza's position!
[KING COLD] Excellent! Have him
brought on board immediately!
[KING COLD]
Status report, Doctor.
[DOCTOR] Your Highness, we
are working on Lord Frieza
around the clock,
and I am confident
that we can rebuild him!
We have the technology to
make him faster, stronger,
and in every way more
powerful than he was before!
Even as we speak, a team
of our brightest engineers
is working diligently to create
the cybernetic attachments,
we will need in order to
make Lord Frieza whole again!
[DOCTOR] Once these mechanical
enhancements have been made
to his existing body,
he will be able to realize
energy levels far greater
than ever before!
Levels that would have
been unsustainable
in his purely organic form!
Sire, I can whole heartedly
assure you that Lord Frieza
will soon reestablish himself
as the most powerful force
in the universe!
There!
[DOCTOR]
Not too quickly, my lord!
Set a course for Earth, Father!
[KING COLD] Planet Earth?
What ever for, my son?
I'd like to blow it up!
Change course!
[FRIEZA] I will make him
suffer for what he did to me!
I will make this
whole planet suffer!
Yes, do be quick about it!
I'd rather not stay too long
on this pathetic
little mud ball!
Not that I don't
just love it here.
But I still don't see why
we can't simply destroy
the planet right now!
You can be absolutely naughty,
Father. It's impressive.
And here I've always
wondered where I picked up
my knack for it.
I take great pride in the
fact that I have taught you
all the necessary
skills of life.
Use them well.
[FRIEZA]
Indeed I will.
For it just so happens
that I have also learned
from you the fine
art of revenge.
Allow me to demonstrate
by vaporizing all
of the Saiyan's
friends, one by one.
[FRIEZA laughing]
And, my! Oh, my! Won't he be
surprised when he returns home
and finds no one here
to welcome him but me?!
[GOHAN grunts]
[YAMCHA thinking] Why me?
I mean, I just got wished back
and now I have to face Frieza?
[VEGETA grunts]
[YAMCHA] I-I don't think
I can do this, you guys!
[BOTH gasping]
[FRIEZA] Now all of you,
begin your search!
And when you find
them, show no mercy!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[FRIEZA, KING COLD gasp]
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[FRIEZA, KING COLD]
Hm...
Ah, so you must be Frieza!
[NARRATOR]
Who is this myterious stranger?
And does he really think
he has what it takes
to go head-to-head with Frieza?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!