[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan felt sure he had failed,
and that the
Earth would soon be lost.
But then came a voice.
[GOKU]
You've got to be joking!
Giving up already?
Well, that's nothing
like the Gohan I know!
Dad, where are you?
[NARRATOR] Teleporting Cell
to King Kai's planet
before the monster
self-destructed,
Goku managed to save the
Earth from certain doom...
...at the cost of his own life.
Trust yourself, Gohan. It may
feel like Cell weakened you,
but what's really draining all
your strength is your own doubt.
Okay! It's all starting
to become clear now, Dad.
I only have one arm,
but that's all I need!
[NARRATOR] Revitalized by his
father's vote of confidence,
Gohan buckled down
for one last run,
powering up to fire
Goku's own choice technique,
the deadly Kamehameha Wave!
Kaa...
Meeh...
[NARRATOR]
The two explosive fighters
have taken their stances,
with power levels
shooting far beyond
anything the Earth
has ever seen.
It's the final
shoot-out between giants
and one thing is for sure,
only one will survive the day!
--[GOKU] Meeh...
--[GOHAN] Meeh...
Now you die!
That's way too big!
Let's go!
Gohan.
[CELL cackles]
[KRILLIN screams]
They're gonna change the
shape of the whole planet!
Cell!
Oh! There's no use trying
to get away from him!
[MR. SATAN] It's a trick!
It's all a trick, I swear!
Someday I'll bring it
all to light! I will!
I can't believe that
you're still saying that!
[screaming]
Cell's decided
to kill us all now!
There's no hope
for us I tell ya'!
[DENDE] Cell is stronger
than ever before!
I hate to believe it, but not
even Gohan can fight him now!
I wasn't a good guardian!
I couldn't protect the Earth!
[CHICHI]
Gohan!
[GOKU]
Gohan! Hang in there!
This must be hard for you
with all those wounds.
I'm sure this makes them burn!
Gohan's losing it.
He's being overtaken.
And now this
is where you end!
I must admit, your kid
is one doozy of a fighter!
[GOKU]
What's the matter, Gohan?
You already have
all the power you need!
Just bring it out!
I can't! I can't keep this up!
I just can't hack it, Dad!
It's too much for me
to handle, I'm just a kid!
I haven't changed! Not at all!
[GOKU] Will you stop
attacking yourself?!
I don't know where you
got it in your head that
there's something wrong
with you, 'cause there's not!
You've saved my life and our
friends' lives so many times
And you're going to
do it again! Right now!
What on Earth are
you mumbling about?
Chanting a little
prayer before you die?
[GOKU]
Let it out, Gohan! Do it now!
[TIEN]
It's huge!
[YAMCHA]
They just won't give it up!
One will!
You fool!
Don't you realize yet you're
up against the perfect weapon!
No way!
Too strong!
[GOKU] Now what?! I've already
told him to give all he's got!
Wait! What if he's still--
[GOKU]
Gohan!
If anywhere in your
mind you're holding back
because you're worried about
the planet, forget about it!
[GOKU] All the damage
you do to the Earth
can be fixed with
the Dragon Balls!
So don't hold
anything back! Got it?
Yeah, but I...
Yes! I can feel you slipping!
Gohan.
I'm coming, Gohan!
No wait!
[KRILLIN]
Piccolo!
He's really gonna
go through with it!
Masenko-ha!
Piccolo...
Piccolo!
Go...
Go-Gohan...
[VEGETA]
That's right! Good, Piccolo!
Where did Piccolo's brain go?
To think he could save
Gohan all by himself!
[TIEN] He didn't think he could,
but he tried to anyway!
[YAMCHA]
Oh, I get it!
Tien! Don't tell me you're gonna
go and pull a Piccolo on me!
Sorry, Krillin, but it's
just not my style
to wait for death without
putting up a decent fight!
Because you're a man of honor,
and a little pigheaded!
Maybe so, but I've
always liked the sound,
of that honor excuse more.
Hey, Krillin, I'll leave
Trunks with you.
Now you're going?!
Let's roll!
[KRILLIN] I guess playing
it safe is one thing
we'll never learn!
[KRILLIN] I hope you
and Trunks will be fine
on your own for now!
You know, 18, it really
was nice seeing you again!
Even if it was
for just a moment!
Foolish, really! I mean it's not
like they'll make a difference!
[GOKU] Dig deeper, Gohan!
It's still not enough!
These are your
last minutes, boy!
So try to make them count!
[PICCOLO]
Special Beam Cannon!
Tri-beam!
Haaa!
Please, guys! Not too
close! Be careful!
[GOKU] Gohan! They can
take care of themselves!
Focus on your energy, Son!
I'm trying!
Would you stop interfering?!
Could this actually work?
You're all so anxious
to die, aren't you?!
Well all you
had to do was ask!
[GOHAN]
He hurt them...
He hurt them!
[GOHAN yells]
No, Gohan, I won't let you
die all alone out there.
'Cause, kid, you were the first
person to ever show me what
it means to have a friend.
Don't know why
I'm getting up again...
It'd be much
easier to keel over!
I know back in the day,
I never would've done this!
Guess I only have
Goku and Gohan to blame!
Those two guys really
changed me for keeps.
And you know, someday,
I'll get them for that.
[TIEN] Surpassing Goku
has been my goal
ever since I became
a Martial Artist.
Without him, there's no way
I would've come this far!
And how did I repay him? I stood
there and watched him die!
I will not make the same
mistake with his son!
[YAMCHA] Goku, I hope you know
how great a kid you've got!
Like father, like son, right?
Well, I won't let you down!
[VEGETA] It's not fear
that's holding me back!
It's... it's just...
[CELL] Why can't you
people just stay down?
Gohan! Raise it higher!
You can win this one!
They just keep
lining up to die!
[VEGETA yells]
No chance! You have no chance!
Oh, no! The Earth
is gonna blow!
Gohan!
We tried!
We're all sorry, Goku!
We all did our very best
to be heroes like you but--
Just not enough!
[DENDE]
Gohan!
You can't take my
Gohan away from me!
He's my baby and no one
can take him away!
Right! You can't take him
'cause he's Goku's son!
He can't be beaten!
[GOKU] Release it, Gohan!
Release everything!
Remember all the
pain he's caused!
The people's he's hurt!
Now make that your power!
Say goodbye!
Vegeta!
Now's your chance!
[GOHAN yells]
[CELL screams]
[CELL]
I'm perfect!
[CELL screams]
[GOHAN panting]
He... did it!
Cell's energy has
completely vanished!
But, you mean we're
really safe again?
Yeah, bud, it looks like it!
Oh man. It's been a few years
since the last time
I heard someone say that.
[CHICHI] He did it!
He did it! My Gohan did it!
[KING KAI] Well, Goku,
your war is finally over.
[GOKU]
Yeah...
Gohan, I'm so proud of you.
[GOHAN chuckles]
[NARRATOR] At last,
the terror known as Cell
has been silenced forever.
The battle is won, and the
world is safe once more.
Thank you, Goku,
for all that you gave.
The Earth will miss you.