[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku and the others entered
an underground spaceship
in a bid to foil the wizard
Babidi's plans to revive
Majin Buu, an evil being
of immeasurable power!
After surviving the
first two stages
of the battle, Goku, Vegeta
and Gohan were awaiting
the commencement of Stage Three,
while their opponent,
Dabura, was making his own
preparations for the showdown!
Known as the King
of the Demon World,
no mortal has ever survived
a fight with Dabura!
And once fully energized,
this fearsome champion
of darkness was ready
to wreak havoc on Goku
and the others as
their next opponent!
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, back at the
World Martial Arts Tournament,
an epic struggle
was taking place
between Number 18
and Mighty Mask as they duked
it out in a righteous rumble!
[NARRATOR]
The battle was evenly matched
until 18 launched an
attack that had Mighty Mask
coming apart at the seams!
Hey, look! Is that Goten?
[NARRATOR] Goten and Trunks
decided to continue
fighting after the
split but the word
from the judge's chair was "No!"
And the two delinquent
members of Mighty Mask
were disqualified!
Now only two competitors remain!
Will 18 become the first
female World Champion
in the history
of the tournament,
or will Mister Satan
manage to hold onto
his title for another year?!
Stay tuned to find out!
[CROWD cheering]
[whimpering]
[GROUP A cheering]
All right! Go, Mister Satan!
[GROUP B]
Yeah! 18! Do it, girl!
Wow!
Whoever thought that
18 was going to get
blown away was mistaken!
This young lady with
a number for a name
has incredible talent!
Can she topple
the World Champion
and become the new
"number one under the sun"?
Only one of these
fighters can walk away
with the title and the grand
prize of 10,000,000 zeni!
Which one is it going to be?!
[MR. SATAN]
What am I gonna do?
I can't beat her! I'm doomed!
[GROUP A cheers]
Yeah! Mister Satan, you rock!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
--[CROWD cheers]
--[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[MR. SATAN groans]
I'm gonna be humiliated!
I'll be the laughing stock
of the whole nation!
No, the whole world!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[GROUP A]
Awesome! Right on! Yeah!
[GROUP B]
Boo! We want 18!
Yeah! Come on, girl!
Let's get it on! Right now!
[CHICHI] Isn't your
Mommy lucky, Maron?!
If she wins she's going
to be a millionaire!
Yay! All right!
They can finally pay rent!
Hey, do you really think this
is the right time
to be celebrating?
I'm worried about
Goku and Gohan!
Why would they leave
at a time like this!
[YAMCHA, MARON, CHICHI,
BULMA, BYSTANDERS] Huh?!
You've got a point there!
Thanks, boys.
That'll be all for now.
Well, what's the hold-up
there, little lady?!
You're scared, aren't ya?
[ANDROID 18]
Wrong!
[yelps]
[whimpers]
[ANDROID 18]
Hmph.
[whimpers]
[yelps]
[ANDROID 18]
Hm!
[screams]
Huh?
[MR. SATAN]
Uh, huh?
[whimpers]
[yelps]
[screams]
I don't wanna die!
Please don't hurt me!
Come on, please! I got a kid! I
just wanna live! Oh my! Please!
Shut up, or I'll
rip your head off!
But then I'd be doing
you a favor, wouldn't I?!
[MR. SATAN]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Look at that!
A perfect head-lock!
It looks like Mister
Satan's in trouble!
[ANDROID 18] So! Do ya still
wanna win this match, big guy?
[MR. SATAN]
Eeeeh!
No! Please! I don't
care about winning!
Just don't hurt me! I beg you!
[GROUP A] Hey! What's
going on? Knock her out!
Now that you know you can't win,
I don't mind letting
you have the victory!
Uh, heh. That tickles my ear.
What?! What did you say?!
I said I wouldn't mind
letting you win
this match, moron!
Huh?!
All ya have to do is
give me 20,000,000 zeni
for letting you win!
Not bad, huh?
I think it's a pretty good deal!
Especially considering
the embarrassing
situation you're in!
[ANNOUNCER]
Would ya look at this, folks!
Wow! Mister Satan's not moving!
What an extraordinary
technique this must be
to subdue a man of his strength!
You... You don't really
mean it, do you?!
[ANDROID 18]
Of course, I mean it!
I don't want all the
publicity and fanfare!
Just give me the
10,000,000 that you'll get
for winning this
match and another ten
out of your own pocket!
[MR. SATAN]
B-But...
There are other
options, you know!
You could fight and get
knocked out and go home
with a big lump on your
head without the title!
No! Anything but that!
[CROWD yelling]
[GROUP A] Get outta here,
ya loser! Man, you stink!
Humph!
Some champion you are!
You're a disgrace, Dad!
That's all you are!
A big disgrace!
[MAN 1]
What a loser!
[WOMAN 1]
He's just a poser!
[CHILD]
He a loser! I don't like him!
[MR. SATAN whimpering]
What's it gonna be?!
Yes, I'll do anything to win!
I'll give you the prize
money plus 10,000,000!
Great! It's settled then!
Good choice, champ!
--[ANDROID 18 yelps]
--[MR. SATAN gasps]
[CROWD]
Ooh!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
What a kick!
It was so fast, you
couldn't even see it!
Amazing! Mister Satan's
back in the match!
[ANDROID 18]
You dog!
That kick was pure luck!
You're goin' down, pal!
Uh, ha, ha!
[laughs]
[grunting]
I've studied and
learned your technique
and made adjustments!
You've put up a good fight,
but now, Mister Satan's
takin' control!
[GROUP A cheers]
I heard that!
No mercy, Mister Satan!
I can't believe an amateur
like you got in here!
You're standin' in the
lion's den, sister!
And you really think
you've got what it takes
to tame the king of the jungle?!
[CROWD B]
Yay! Go, 18!
Stop talking and
start fighting, now!
Oh! Right! Sure!
[yells]
[MR. SATAN grunting]
[ANNOUNCER]
What an amazing counter-attack!
Whoa! Mister Satan's going wild!
Folks! Have you ever
seen anything like it!
Look at those punches!
[MISTER SATAN grunting]
--[ANDROID 18 grunts]
--[MISTER SATAN groans]
But...
You said you were
gonna lose on purpose!
I'm going to, but we have to
make it look good for
the fans, don't we?
Besides, what was
it you called me?
An "amateur"?
Sorry! I was just trying
to act like myself!
Accepted!
Now pick me up and
throw me across the arena!
Then finish me off with some
special technique of yours!
Well? Do it!
Oh! Right!
[MR. SATAN grunts]
Wow! What a throw!
He just chuncked 18
like a rag-doll!
[laughs] Alright!
The Ultra Megaton Punch!
[GROUP A]
Yeah! Go for it!
[yells]
Comin' at ya, sweetheart!
No more foolin' around!
Feel my true power!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[CROWD gasps]
Right smack in the head!
[GROUP A gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
Uh...
Ehh, what? Oh, no!
Are you telling me
that that's the best
you could come up with?
Well... Yes! I'm afraid so!
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
Ugh... Why me?!
[ANDROID 18 groans]
[CROWD gasps]
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[ANNOUNCER] It appears
that in a delayed reaction
to Mister Satan's Megaton Punch,
18 has been knocked
out of the arena!
I'm not sure how to
explain it though!
I did it!
For years I've been trying
to perfect a variation
of the Megaton Punch
that uses latent energy
to cause a delayed reaction
to catch my opponent off-guard!
And today, it finally happened!
It worked!
After ten years of
practicing every day, it worked!
Yeah!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
Huh?! What am I doing?!
Mister Satan's the winner!
This is fantastic!
Mister Satan retains his title!
[MR. SATAN]
I'm the man!
[yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
What an incredible match!
Years of practicing a
variation of the Megaton Punch
culminated in a blow that has
won the World Championship
and stunned us all!
If I hadn't seen
it with my own eyes,
I wouldn't believe it!
I saw it! But I still
don't believe it!
Yeah! Whoa!
[laughing]
Huh?
Good match!
I'll be paying your house
a little visit tomorrow!
If you don't pay,
I'm going to kill you, champ!
Yes! I, uh, the
champ understands!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen!
For yet another year,
the Champion of the World
is Mister Satan!
[TRUNKS]
Well, there goes Mighty Mask!
He's dead!
He lost his head,
and the Championship!
You're already World Champion!
What do you care?!
But that's Junior Champion!
Huh?
Aw, now what?! Is everyone
flying nowadays?!
[GOTEN]
Wow! Who could it be?!
Hey! It's Videl!
Yo! Videl! Over here!
Huh?
Hey! It's us!
Hey, guys!
[GOTEN]
Hi, Videl!
[TRUNKS]
Wait up!
[VEGETA]
Who do they think they are,
keeping us waiting
so long?! Come on!
I wonder who they're
gonna send out next...
[GOKU]
There's no tellin'!
[GOHAN]
Man, this is kinda like
bein' on a game
show or somethin'!
I wonder who's gonna be
behind door number 3.
I'm kinda excited!
I can't wait to see how much
you've progressed
over the years!
Huh?
Yeah!
You were just a boy
when you defeated Cell!
I'll bet you're
twice as strong now!
Yeah, well...
I'm... Uh...
Not quite as strong
as I was then!
Gohan's been far too
busy going to school
and going out on dates
to do any serious training!
Both of us are more powerful
than he is in his condition!
[GOHAN]
Eh, ha, ha...
Of course, I could be wrong!
Maybe he's been training in
between classes or during P.E.
or something! Maybe he's
the strongest one here!
[GOHAN]
Well...
[VEGETA]
I didn't think so!
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
This is amazing!
As strong as these three are,
they're not even
at their maximum!
But why wasn't I
able to see this?!
I'm the Supreme Kai!
How could mere mortals
from the lower world
have this kind of potential
without me being aware of it?!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
[VEGETA]
Hm?
[SUPREME KAI]
What? Impossible!
[cackles]
It's Dabura!
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
I-I can't believe that Babidi
would send him so soon!
It's only Stage Three!
[DABURA]
I must say, I'm impressed!
Beating Yakon and advancing
to Stage Three is far beyond
what any other mortal
has managed to do!
Yes! It was quite
unexpected indeed!
So now you must face me...
Which means, you will
progress no further.
Hm! Your boss must be nervous
if he sent out his
number one guy!
Why doesn't he
come himself, huh?
He too scared?
[gasps]
Let's dispense
with the idle talk,
I'd prefer it if you'd just
attack! All of you, together!
Hey! Wait a second!
It's my turn to fight and
that's what I'm gonna do!
Impudent fool!
This is a lousy
place to have a fight,
though, it's way too small!
A secluded place in the
mountains sounds good
or maybe a nice
spot on the beach!
Wait! No!
Then we'll get
sand in our boots!
[gasping]
[growls] Bah! Silence child...
Haaaa!
You will fight me here and now!
[BABIDI]
Dabura, wait a second!
Huh?!
[GOHAN]
Hm?
[BABIDI] I was just
thinking and it might not
be such a bad idea to pick
another location for the fight!
You see, to revive Buu,
we're going to need
the spaceship intact!
Yes... I understand!
[BABIDI]
Any preferences?
Perhaps a planet
similar to this one!
I don't want an
unfair advantage!
[giggles] Dear me!
You really want to show them,
don't you, Dabura!
Very well! As you wish!
Here goes!
Ooooh!
Papparapa!
[GOHAN]
Huh?!
Ahh! What's this?!
Well, then!
Let's begin, shall we?!
Sure!
Gohan! Stay focused!
[GOHAN]
Right, Dad!
[GOHAN grunts]
[DABURA]
Hmm...
[DABURA, GOHAN grunting]
[VIDEL] So this strange man
told them that he needed
their help to stop the wizard
who's trying to revive
this evil monster
Buu with his magic.
So that's where your dads are!
And Gohan went with 'em!
[GOTEN] Then the whole
world's in danger!
[TRUNKS] Yeah! T-They're
gonna have to fight!
[VIDEL]
Huh?
[GOTEN]
Wow! Magic?!
[VIDEL]
Yes, that's what the man said!
A wizard?!
[VIDEL]
Uh-huh!
Can you believe it!
Cool! This is major!
Way major!
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
Huh?!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
You know what this means...?!
We get to save the world!
Uhh, boys?!
[GOTEN]
They went that way, right?
[TRUNKS]
Yeah!
I hope it's not too far,
or we'll never catch 'em!
You guys aren't going, are you?!
It's dangerous over there!
Hey, yo!
If we don't hurry, we could
miss the whole thing!
Let's get a move on!
I don't wanna miss it!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's goooo!
Yeah!
--[GOTEN] Yay!
--[TRUNKS] Woo-hoo!
[TRUNKS]
We're gonna kick some boo-tay!
Insane.
[DABURA yells]
[DABURA laughs]
[GOHAN grunts]
[DABURA grunts]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[GOHAN]
Woooh! That was close!
[DABURA laughs]
[DABURA grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
The fool!
Huh?!
[grunts]
[DABURA grunts]
--[GOHAN grunts]
--[DABURA groans]
[gasps]
[DABURA grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[DABURA cackles]
[DABURA groans]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Look out Dabura!
With Gohan turning
up the flames,
it looks like the battle
is about to get serious!
Who will prove the
victor of Stage Three?!
Find out next Dragon Ball Z!