[NARRATOR] On the last episode
of Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu was on a manhunt
for Goku and Vegeta,
and when his search led him
to the great Kai Planet,
life in Other World took
a turn for the worse.
[KRILLIN grunts]
[grunts]
[NARRATOR] Vegeta wanted to
lure Buu away from the planet
before he destroyed it,
but Goku wasn't sure how.
[VEGETA]
Oh, use your brain, Kakarot.
All we have to do is
raise our power levels,
and he'll come running.
Of course!
Right!
Buu squash you like bugs!
[NARRATOR] Hearing their call,
Buu didn't waste a moment,
but went directly to the sacred
land of the Supreme Kai,
where the battle is
about to begin!
[laughs]
[ALL gasp]
[chuckles] How perfect!
We can fight as we like here.
[GOKU]
Hm.
Please leave now, you guys.
If you try to stay, you'll
only be helping Majin Buu.
[KIBITO KAI]
What?
[GOKU] Sorry, but we can't fight
to our full potential
if we're worried
about your safety.
Oh yeah, I understand now.
I know what's going on here!
Sure, you're thinking
that our sacred planet
is going to be demolished
during the fight.
Oh well, kick some
butt, you two.
Thanks, Old Kai.
Do your best, Vegeta,
and you, too, Goku!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[DENDE thinking]
Goku...
Grab a hold of me, you two.
I believe it's time
for us to go.
[OLD KAI]
I don't know about this!
You'll be just fine.
[screams]
Where are we?
I've transported us to a
planet in the physical plane,
quite far from the action
is taking place.
We'll be safe here.
[OLD KAI] You could've picked
a place with shorter grass.
Oh well, too late!
Those Saiyans
are a stubborn lot!
Why did they have to destroy
those earrings we gave them?
I guess they plan on using the
Fusion Technique to fight Buu.
But can they get the
job done in half an hour?
Well... I doubt it, but at
least they'll have a chance.
Hey, we should
probably decide now,
while we still have
a spare minute.
[VEGETA] Right! How are
we going to do it?
[GOKU] I guess we'll try
the old fashioned way.
[VEGETA] All right, Kakarot,
you're asking for it.
[GOKU]
We'll see about that!
[GOKU, VEGETA]
Rock! Paper!
[gasping]
[VEGETA, GOKU] Ready!
Rock! Paper! Scissors! Haa!
Yeah! I did it!
[groans]
That's not the Fusion Technique!
Those idiots! What in the
world are they doing?!
Have they finally gone mad?
[VEGETA]
Yeah, you beat me, Kakarot,
but there's a good chance
that I'll get my turn anyway!
Gee, thanks,
but if you wanted a turn,
you should have chose paper!
[GOKU]
The fact of the matter is,
I probably could have
destroyed the fat Majin Buu
when I was at
Super Saiyan Three,
but I wanted Gohan and
the boys to try their hand
at saving the world.
I won't be around forever.
And, neither will he, hopefully.
All right, Buu! Let's do it!
What's the deal?
Did he drop something?
Huh?!
[snores]
[yells]
[GOKU] That bum, he's sound
asleep! How dare he!
No, this can't go on anymore!
He's killed too many innocent
people. It's not right!
[yells]
Hm?!
[yells, whoops]
[laughing]
What in the world?
[KABITO KAI]
Ahh! Oh, no! What have we done?
We forgot to bring
that other man and his dog
with us when we left!
[OLD KAI]
That poor dog.
[KID BUU whoops]
Uhh... Huh?
[BUU whoops]
He's back. Phooey.
Hey! It's you, boy!
[barks]
[MR. SATAN groaning]
Oh, Bee, this Buu
has a screw loose.
[KID BUU whooping]
[YAMCHA]
Where are they?
[KRILLIN]
Shh! He's searching!
[KING KAI]
Mm...
Yeah! Now I can see them!
Good, where are they, King Kai?
[KING KAI]
The planet you're seeing
is the sacred land of the Kais,
the abode of Supreme Kai.
Even us lower Kais
have a difficult
time reaching that place!
I doubt Buu would have ever
found that planet on his own.
They must have lured him there.
Probably to prevent
him from destroying us.
[YAMCHA] With Goku there,
it wouldn't surprise me.
Hey! What is all this nonsense
that you're babbling
about, Northy?
Huh? What nonsense? Take a look.
You've got eye's to see,
you lazy old kook!
[grunts]
[KING KAI] Move your antenna
a little to the right!
--There! That's it!
--[OLIBU gasps]
[whooping]
Fool! Who does he think he is?
Forget this, I've had enough.
[GOKU grunts]
[muffled grunting]
[whoops]
[GOKU grunts]
[KID BUU growls]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[KID BUU groans]
[growls]
Huh?!
--[KID BUU screams]
--[GOKU yells]
Yeah! He did it, boy!
Majin Buu is history!
Goku!
Fantastic! I knew Goku
would do it! He's the man!
Is Buu really gone for good?
I'm afraid not, Buu isn't one
to be defeated by that
level of attack.
[laughs]
Presto!
[laughing continues]
Aaah, you rat!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU, KID BUU grunting]
Great balls of fire, Bee!
When is this dream gonna end?
[BEE barks]
[GOKU grunts]
--[GOKU groaning]
--[KID BUU grunting, laughs]
Ah!
[screams]
That beast! I don't
care if this is a dream,
I want that Buu to lose!
Tear him up, blonde dude! Yeah!
[screams]
[whooping]
[whooping continues]
Huh?!
[yells]
Wow. This is good.
This is great!
The best I've seen!
Northy, isn't that
the guy named Goku
who trained here not long ago?
Yep! That's him!
The same fighter who beat
Pikkon in the big tournament.
He's gotten a lot stronger
since then though, as you see.
Who's in pink?
Silly, that's Buu.
You faught him yourself
a long time ago, remember?
Hello? He was wreaking
havoc all over the Universe?
Total destruction, a mess!
[yells]
You've got to be
kidding me! That's him?!
That's Bibidi's mad man?!
He's been revived again?!
This is terrible!
[KING KAI]
Mm-hm.
We're lucky to
be alive right now.
No offense, Pikkon,
but he's a lot stronger.
[PIKKON grunts]
[WEST KAI]
It's true!
Okay, on to Plan B,
whatever that is.
--[GOKU grunts]
--[KID BUU] Ah!
[MR. SATAN, BEE whimpering]
I hope they're having fun,
because I'm not!
[whimpers]
Ancestor, you're shaking
like a leaf. What's wrong?
[laughs]
[growls]
Great! Now what's he up to?
Better not wait to find out!
[GOKU yells]
[gasps]
[KID BUU yells]
Ah! [groaning]
[yells]
[growls]
[GOKU]
Uh-oh!
[chuckles]
[whimpers]
[VEGETA]
Where are you, Kakarot?
Freaky.
[KID BUU chuckles]
[gasps]
[KID BUU laughs]
--[MR. SATAN groaning]
--[BEE whimpering]
[laughing]
[laughs]
It's all over!
Majin Buu is too strong!
I don't wanna see
Goku get hurt!
[OLD KAI] Now, now,
I wouldn't count Goku out yet!
You can still see
fire in his face, look!
[KABITO KAI, DENDE gasp]
That's not the look
of a desperate man.
That's the face
of a true champion!
[whimpers]
Is it over? The dream!
Tell me it's over, boy!
[screams]
[MR. SATAN] Someone wake me up!
I can't take it anymore!
Darn you!
Where's your weak point?
You're twice as strong
as you were before!
Your speed, your power.
[laughs]
There, you see? I told you,
he's pulling out the stops.
[yells]
Heh. So Kakarot's finally
in the mood, is he?
[VEGETA thinking] This ought
to be one to remember.
[GOKU]
Majin Buu, your time has come!
[gasps, chuckles]
[NARRATOR] The battle that will
decide the fate of the Universe
is about to begin in earnest!
Can Super Saiyan Three Goku
topple the infamous Majin Buu?
Next time, on Dragon Ball Z!