[DR. GERO groaning]
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
the diabolical Dr. Gero's evil
plans were short circuited
by one of his
own killer creations.
Trunks, the boy from the future,
had predicted the
doctor's demise
but this bizarre turn
of events sent everyone's
head spinning --
especially the doctor's!
The black-haired
Android 17 took control
and with the help of the
blonde beauty, Android 18,
the digital duo
unleashed a third android.
Perhaps the most
dangerous of them all.
This new hi-tech
titan revealed that
the recently disconnected
doctor had programmed him
for one purpose only --
to destroy Goku!
But Vegeta, fueled by his
extra large ego and his new
Super Saiyan
powers, caught up
with the fearsome
threesome on the highway.
Now it's up to Vegeta
to pull the plug on this
hi-tech triple threat.
But can he do it alone?
Find out today!
[VEGETA]
Okay, which one of you do I send
to the scrap heap first?!
He talks too much.
Alright, I'll show him!
So it's ladies first is it?
Well that's just fine with me!
Don't expect me
to go easy on you,
'cause I fight to win.
[ANDROID 17]
This should be interesting.
[birds chirping]
[VEGETA grunts]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
Good!
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
[ANDROID 18]
For your sake, I hope you can
do better than that!
[ANDROID 18] I may have
to increase my strength
to full power!
[VEGETA grunting]
Look at that...
Dr. Gero's
information was wrong.
Vegeta is much stronger
than we originally thought!
But could he win?
I doubt it!
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[VEGETA] Ooh! For someone made
of metal, you move pretty fast.
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] If you give up now,
I promise I'll turn you into
something practical, like a
toaster or a washing machine.
[ANDROID 18] He is really
starting to annoy me.
I'll have to give his
attitude an adjustment.
[ANDROID 17]
Ooh! Look at Vegeta.
He's following 18.
Following her right into a trap.
Gohan...
How much longer will it be
till we get home? I'm tired!
Hang on, Yajirobi. We'll
be there real soon, okay?
Hey! Stop your complaining!
We're tired too!
But I can't stand it!
[YAJIROBE groans]
I'm, so hungry...
And I'm cold.
Gross! That's kinda rude!
Trunks, Oh, you're being
such a good boy!
[BABY TRUNKS babbling]
[YAJIROBE groaning]
[BULMA laughs]
[BABY TRUNKS laughing]
Man! He sprung a leak!
[YAJIROBE] Ew! Ick! Yuck! Ugh!
Does anyone have a tissue...
[GOHAN]
Quit movin' around Yajirobe!
Do you wanna fall off?
Sit still, will ya!
Hey watch it! Cut that out--
[SHEPHERD] Aw nuts! Nothing
ever happens around here.
I'm so bored.
[SHEPHERD]
Hm?
[VEGETA growls]
That's it!
[SHEPHERD whimpering]
[SHEPHERD screams]
[SHEPHERD]
Ma was right.
I should've stayed
in dental school.
[KRILLIN] I hope we can
catch up to Vegeta before
he runs into those androids.
Or else he's history.
[TRUNKS] Father, why
wouldn't you listen to me?
[rattling]
[CLETUS]
Hm? Huh?
[OTIS] What are you
lookin' at, Cletus?
[CLETUS] You ain't gonna
believe this, Otis, but there's
two people standing on top o'
your rig at this very moment!
[OTIS] Yeah right, I think
you been on the road
too long, little buddy!
What's wrong?
Batteries getting low?
Darnn! Slow driver! Move!
[VEGETA grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[CAR DRIVER 1 screams]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
What was that?
[VEGETA grutns]
[CAR DRIVER 3 screams]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA grunts]
[CAR DRIVER 2 screams]
[VEGETA growls]
[ANDROID 18 laughs]
[VEGETA] That's the last
time you get away from me!
Look they've come back!
[ANDROID 18]
Did you enjoy the ride?
Your warranty ran out
with me a long time ago,
so you're going to be recycled.
[ANDROID 18 laughs]
Now! Be good and be still!
[VEGETA]
I'm going to wipe that smirk off
your pretty little
face of yours.
[TRUCKER BOB screams]
[VEGETA] You've laughed at me
for the last time, Android.
What are you doing in
the middle of the road?!
Are you guys nuts? Move it!
[TRUCKER BOB]
I got a truck load of paperclips
I gotta get unloaded!
So get out of the way!
Any last words
before I blast you?
[TRUCKER BOB] Excuse me!
Big truck? Paperclips? Come on!
Take your best shot!
[VEGETA growls]
Hey!
[VEGETA grunts]
[TRUCKER BOB whimpering]
[ANDROID 17] Now that's what
I like to see. Destruction!
[ANDROID 18]
That was just so poor.
Your aim was off by 10 degrees!
[ANDROID 18 laughing]
[ANDROID 18]
What's the matter?
Did you have
something in your eye?
[VEGETA growls]
You can be very quick when
you want to be, Android.
[VEGETA] But your speed won't
save you from me for long.
[ANDROID 18]
Don't worry, Vegeta.
I don't plan on running
from you anymore.
[MARON laughing]
[MASTER ROSHI] Oh my, this
is a fascinating article.
[MASTER ROSHI laughing]
[MARON]
Hey Turtle! Look at me!
Hello!
[MASTER ROSHI]
Those are some dangerous curves!
Oh my, I'm beginning
to feel dizzy...
Blood rushing to head!
[MASTER ROSHI grunting]
Hey! Turtle!
Oh? Hi there! Hey!
[MASTER ROSHI]
Looking good!
[MARON] Leave that old man on
the beach and come and join me!
[MARON giggles]
Turtle's so cute!
Come on in!
Come on in?
[TURTLE laughing]
Don't be shy!
[MARON]
Okay, see you later!
[MASTER ROSHI]
Why you!
[MASTER ROSHI growls]
[TURTLE gasps]
[MASTER ROSHI cackles]
Face it, I'm a lot stronger
than you'll ever be!
I doubt it.
You're so weak, I won't
have to even break a sweat!
[ANDROID 18] For your
information I've been
taking it easy on you.
I know how fragile
you flesh and blood
types can be.
[VEGETA] Oh really!
Well don't do me any favors!
Because I guarantee you, I won't
be showing you any mercy!
Hm. Well Okay!
[VEGETA gasps, grunts]
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGETA coughs]
[VEGETA gasping]
[ANDROID 18]
Tell me, Vegeta. I'm curious...
[ANDROID 18] What is it like
to feel this kind of pain?
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[VEGETA groans]
[ANDROID 18]
I know I'm being hard on you,
but it's the only
way you'll learn.
[ANDROID 17]
Hm.
Hm?
Are you okay in there Vegeta?
[VEGETA weakly] Of course
I am! Why wouldn't I be?
Hm?
You're all right!
[VEGETA laughs] Of course!
That was just a lucky punch.
[VEGETA]
What are you doing here?
I told you I don't need your
help and I don't want it either!
[ANDROID 17]
Look at that!
Vegeta's friends have
come to his aid!
Android 18 can take care
of them all by herself
but maybe I should help her.
Unless, you might want to?
What do you say, 16?
You up for a fight?
No, I will not fight them.
You won't? Is something
wrong with you, man?
So, you're just gonna stand
there like a statue, is that it?
I told you. I will
only fight with Goku!
Alright...
Have it your way, pal.
[ANDROID 17] But I sugget you
loosen up before you rust!
Uh-oh... There's another android
approaching at 12 o'clock.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
It's time to get out of here.
We should leave now
and come back when Goku is
better! Then we'll fight them!
What is wrong with you?
Run away? I'm staying!
You should listen
to your friend.
He's the one who will have
to clean you off the highway.
Are you kidding me?
You want me to leave now,
when we're just getting
to know each other?
You should be so lucky.
I fight alone. I don't
need the help of anyone
and that includes
these Earthlings,
the Namec and most
of all Kakarot!
I am the most powerful
Saiyan who has ever lived!
[VEGETA] I fear no one!
Especially not this android!
[clapping]
A beautiful speech.
I can see it now.
You truly are a prince with
the royal blood of a Saiyan!
[VEGETA]
Stay out of this one, Android!
I'll deal with
you soon enough.
Once I've finished with her.
Well, I'd hate to deny
you the opportunity
to test your
strength against 18.
So, I'll make a deal with you.
[ANDROID 17] I'm willing to
stand aside and let you fight
as long as you fight alone.
But if any one of these
'friends' of yours tries to
assist you in any way, well...
I'll be forced to step in.
[VEGETA] You don't have
to worry about this group.
They're a bunch of cowards.
They won't risk
their lives for me!
Then, you agree?
[VEGETA]
Yes, I agree.
[ANDROID 18]
Then let's continue?
Bring it on!
As you wish!
[grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[ANDROID 18 yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA laughs]
What's the matter?
You look a bit ruffled.
Yes, well...
Looks aren't everything.
You fight quite well for
being such a little man.
It's impressive, even
if you are a Saiyan!
[VEGETA]
I know.
There are few willing
to train as intensely
as I did to achieve
this kind of power.
How sad. To work so hard for...
...so little.
Sad for you!
[grunting]
[KRILLIN] What's going on?
I can't see a thing!
[PICCOLO]
Vegeta's on the attack!
[TIEN]
That's it...
Go get her!
Hm?
[grunting]
[TRUNKS]
It's amazing...
I never knew my
father was so strong.
I can't believe he's fighting
that android one-on-one!
[PICCOLO] There's no way
Vegeta can keep fighting
at this intensity!
He's done for...
He can't win!
[TRUNKS, KRILLIN gasp]
[PICCOLO] Look! She's making
him burn up all his energy
and then she's
going to attack him!
[grunting]
Every move, takes its toll!
Vegeta is getting weaker while
the android still stays strong.
[grunting]
[VEGETA groans]
No! Stop!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA groaning]
[KRILLIN]
I wish Goku was here!
He'd know what to do!
[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA yells]
[ANDROID 18] It's time to
put an end to this game,
don't you think?
[VEGETA] She's been toying
with me the whole time!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA groans]
No!
[ALL gasp]
[VEGETA groaning, grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
Father!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[PICCOLO]
Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
Father!
[NARRATOR] This looks like the
beginning of the end for Vegeta.
Even with his
Super Saiyan Strength,
he was still no
match against
the unlimited power
of Android 18.
Now Trunks has
jumped into the fray
but what chance does he
have? Is he about to make
the ultimate sacrifice
for Vegeta?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!