[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
The Cell Games continued,
moving into the most
furious fighting yet.
Goku's Super Saiyan
powers were put to the test
and he passed with
flying colors.
To everyone's surprise,
his awesome power could
barely be contained
in Cell's tournament ring.
Not to be outdone,
Cell went into battle mode
after a quick warm up.
The bio-mechanical
menace was determined
to show the whole world that
he could finally crush
Goku and all the
other challengers.
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR]
With unimaginable strength
and an array of stolen fighting
techniques at his disposal,
Cell has become
a truly fearsome foe!
But Goku is no rookie,
and he, too, was radiating
with pure fighting energy.
As the two figures squared
off, one thing was certain,
the rumble would not
be one to miss.
After an intense exchange,
Cell fired a Kamehameha wave
big enough
to destroy the planet!
But Goku diverted
the blast upward
and used his Instant
Transmission to save himself
at the last moment,
letting the attack
fly safely
into outer space.
[NARRATOR]
Back on the ground,
Goku ended Cell's strong
offensive with a kick,
leaving the never-ending match
at a standoff once again.
And leaving the vicious Cell
with a question he had
to have answered...
[CELL] I want you to tell me
how you are able to
disappear and reappear.
It's my new technique,
Instant Transmission.
[NARRATOR] Cell may not have
Instant Transmission,
but he does have
incredible speed,
and now, he's more
determined than ever
to prove his perfection.
[CELL] Am I too fast
for you, Goku?
[NARRATOR] The fight
between Goku and Cell
is approaching its final round!
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS thinking] Come on, Goku,
you can't let Cell win!
You're the only
one who can beat him now!
[TIEN thinking]
Cell is all over the place!
Goku doesn't have a chance!
[blows landing]
Oh man, Cell's good!
[GOKU growls]
[CELL growls]
[thinking] Goku has lost
his advantage.
--[GOKU growls]
--[PICCOLO grunts]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[grunting continues]
Wow, they're fast!
Look at 'em go!
[VEGETA growls]
[thinking] Try harder, Dad.
I know you can do it.
[CELL snarls]
[GOKU growls]
[ANNOUNCER] Do not adjust
your television sets,
ladies and gentlemen!
These two fighters
really are moving faster
than the human eye
can see, honest!
Uh, say, Champ? These guys
aren't amateurs, are they?
[whimpering]
[CELL growls]
[GOKU grunts,
CELL yells]
Goku!
[grunting,
blows landing]
[ANNOUNCER] Huh? Where's Cell?
[CELL growls]
[ANNOUNCER] Oh no, I can
tell this isn't going to be good
for the ratings.
Uh, guys, can anyone see
where our two fighters went to?
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[GOHAN thinking] There you go,
Dad. Keep moving at his speed.
They vanished! Hey, I have
no earthly idea where they are!
[GOKU growls,
CELL grunts]
[GOKU snarls]
Not a bad fight, Goku!
Perhaps you are worthy
of fighting a warrior
of my supreme stature.
Oh boy!
Too bad all the fights
won't be this good.
Now, let us continue.
There they are!
They're right there in the ring!
They're hiding in
that broken part over there!
It's another
one of their tricks!
[MR. SATAN] See what I mean?!
They're right there, I tell ya!
Sure I do... I see 'em!
You know, when it's
my turn to fight,
I won't be fooled
by those tricks!
Ladies and gentlemen,
remember you heard it here
from Mr. Satan,
our champion!
[GOKU yells]
[ALL yell]
Wow... They're up there!
So, would you say this is
another one of their tricks?
Well, shoot them! Hurry up!
I'll try!
It's still kinda tough
to get a shot, though!
[CROWD murmuring]
Awh, gimme a break! What is
this, the weather channel?!
How are we supposed to know
if it's the end of
the world or not?!
I came here to see a fight!
We want the champ! Mr. Satan!
[ROSHI] Will ya look at that...
The camera can't even
capture their movements!
I just wonder how long Goku can
continue fighting at that pace.
[DENDE]
There's trouble down there,
but I can't seem to focus on it.
My mind is too clouded.
[MR. POPO] Dende,
you sure remind me of Kami.
He used to stand
in that very same spot
as he tried to make
sense of the Earth.
Did he really?
[MR. POPO] Oh yes!
[DENDE whimpers]
There's no need to be upset.
Like the former
guardians before you,
it will take some time
before you are comfortable
with your new role
as guardian of the Earth.
Just relax, Dende.
Stop doubting your own abilities
and start listening
with your mind.
Calm your thoughts.
Now, what do you see?
The tournament is still on,
it's a fierce battle.
See? You did it!
[DENDE] Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Popo.
I know I'll never
be able to replace Kami,
but I will try
my best, I promise.
I just wish there were
something more that I could do,
I feel so helpless!
This tournament will
decide the fate of the Earth,
and all I can do for now is
watch, and leave it to Goku.
[DENDE] I may be this planet's
guardian, but he is its hero.
[blows landing]
[BOTH grunt]
[GOKU yells]
[CELL shouts]
[grunting]
Goku, don't give up!
[PICCOLO growls]
Dad, hang on!
[grunting]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Huh?!
You almost fell out of the ring!
If you had, I would
have been declared the winner
of this little match of ours!
Huh?!
Is the game too hard for you?
Should I make it easier?
Perhaps this will make things
a little more interesting.
[CELL chuckles]
[grunting]
Hold on, what are you doing?
[CELL] I am tired of being
confined to that ring anyway.
Oh, and... you might want
to tell your friends
to clear the area.
[GOKU gasps]
[CELL chuckles]
Hey! Get away from the ring!
NOW!!!
[KRILLIN] Whoa!
Cell blew the ring up!
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[grunting]
[ANNOUNCER] Thanks,
you saved us all.
It is time for all of
you to evacuate, right now.
I don't think so, pal!
The show must go on.
Besides, we still have
to let our champion
have his shot at Cell!
Whatta ya say, Champ?
Ready for action?
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[PIIZA] Hey, Hercule, you okay?
Yeah! Let's get it on!
I could take Cell with
both hands tied behind my back!
[CELL] How do you
like that, Goku?
It's quite an improvement,
don't you think?
[CELL] Now the whole
desert is our ring.
Let's say the last one
standing wins the game.
I see. So it's
a fight to the finish!
[CELL] Would you have it
any other way?
[GOKU] No, I guess not.
[GOKU grunts]
Right. That's enough talk, Goku.
Now it's time
to continue the game.
[GOKU gasps]
[grunting]
[KRILLIN]
Get out of there, Goku!
Quick, shoot!
Come on! Shoot!
Get out there! Hurry!
[LIONEL] Do I get
hazard pay for this?!
[CROWD groans]
[MAN] I can't see a thing!
Is this the end or what?!
[phones ringing]
--[OPERATOR A] ZTV, hold please!
--[OPERATOR B] ZTV, hold please!
--[OPERATOR A] Yes ma'am! No!
--[OPERATOR B] Yes! No, ma'am!
--ZTV, hold please! We're sorry!
--We're sorry, sir...
--ZTV, hold please!
[phone ringing continues,
OPERATORS stammering]
[OPERATORS talking incoherently,
phones ringing]
[OPERATOR B] My uncle owns the
place! Yes, you can quote me!
[OPERATOR A] It's not my fault,
I tell ya!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU grunting]
[screaming]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[VEGETA growls]
Wow! What a big blast!
Sheesh! Hey! Mr. Satan,
how did he do that?!
Yo, speak, Mr. Satan!
Uh, it's a trick!
It's a trick!
[GOKU growls]
[grunting]
[CELL growls]
[GOKU growls]
[yelling]
[CELL snarls]
[BOTH growling]
Um, what's going on?!
The Earth is shaking!
Mr. Satan, this
IS another trick, right?
[MR SATAN screams]
[whimpering]
They're even!
Not only are they
equal in speed,
but now they're equal
in power as well!
[thinking] What is the
secret to Kakarot's power?!
[CELL growling]
[GOKU growling]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
[CELL grunts]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[KING KAI gasps]
Come on... Come on!
[KING KAI] That's it, Goku!
Give him a left!
And a right!
Show Cell who's boss!
Ow! No! Ah! You're hopeless!
Who taught you
how to fight anyway?!
Come on! Keep your guard up!
Yes, that's it! Stick
and jab! Stick and jab!
Oooh, yeah!
Alright! You got him now!
Way to go! Yeah! That's my boy!
[KING KAI laughs]
This fight on Earth
could go on for some time.
Goku and Cell both
possess incredible strength
and neither one of them
would ever think of giving up.
Strange, their power levels
isn't decreasing; it's growing!
[KING KAI] Say, would either of
you care to make a wager
on this tournament...?
[CELL snarls]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU snarling]
[CELL shouting]
[CELL yelling]
[CELL growling]
Hm?!
Look! Goku! He's way up there!
Hey! What's he doing?
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Kaa... Meeh...
Everyone get down!
Take cover! Get moving!
Goku's releasing
the Kamehameha!
[CELL growls]
[laughing]
[CELL] Goku wouldn't dare emit
the Kamehameha wave
attack from there! He'll
destroy the Earth if he does!
[CELL laughs]
Ah, just relax, guys! Goku's
crazy, but he's not that crazy!
There's nothing to worry about!
Haa...
[KRILLIN gasps]
No! Goku?!
[GOKU growls]
No! Don't do it!
Please, Dad, don't!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[VEGETA growls]
No! He wouldn't...
[GOKU grunts]
[CELL gasps]
[GOKU growls]
NOOO!!
HAAA!!
[GOHAN gasps]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[grunting]
[NARRATOR] Has Goku beaten
Cell at his own game?
Fighting at full power and
using the killer combination
of the Kamehameha Wave
with the Instant Transmission
technique really
blew Cell's mind!
The sly Super Saiyan's maneuver
put his friends in a panic,
but the risk seemed
to have paid off!
Now the cruel monster
is out of commission
and the threat
to Planet Earth is over!
...Or is it?