[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the struggle between man and
machine reached new heights
as Goku battled Android 19,
a radically advanced artificial
life form, designed by Dr. Gero
to be the ultimate
fighting machine.
After controlling
the entire fight,
the tables suddenly turned
on Goku and he found himself
at the wrong end of
several punishing blows.
When the going gets tough,
Goku gets going.
But in this case,
the iron-willed Saiyan
was unable to respond.
Most unexpectedly, Goku
was paralyzed with pain
and seemed incapable
of continuing the fight.
[GOHAN] It's that virus! It's
attacking his heart right now!
Father!
Yes! That's it!
[NARRATOR] Trunks' prediction
that Goku would contract
a horrible disease
has finally come true.
But it couldn't have
come at a worse time!
[GOKU grunts]
[grunting continues]
[ANDROID 19] Hmm...
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[KRILLIN] Gosh!
I've never seen Goku like
this before! This is terrible!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOHAN] Daddy!
Gohan, stay...
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO gasps]
Wait a sec. Hey, Trunks,
what happens to me?
Do I die in the battle as well?
Not too long from now,
you're going to catch a new
virus that attacks the heart.
You're going to die from it.
Huh?!
[TRUNKS] It's a radical virus.
You'll start hearing
about it soon.
Not even a Super
Saiyan can beat it.
[GOKU] What a bummer!
Being killed by a stupid virus.
[GOKU growls]
What a waste!
Here you go. Take this,
man. For your health.
My health?
[TRUNKS] It's an antidote.
[GOKU] Hmm...
[TRUNKS] There's no cure
now for that nasty virus
you're going to get,
but in my time there is.
Take this when you get
sick and you'll be fine.
[PICCOLO gasps]
Don't do it, Gohan!
Your dad is still in command
and we can't intervene
until he says so!
But there's one
thing that we can do.
Yeah! We can give
him a Senzu Bean!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[thinking] This is horrible!
I feel like I'm dying!
[GOKU grunts]
[ANDROID 19] Hmph.
[GOKU pants]
Goku! Senzu Bean! Catch!
You're the best, Krillin...
[crunching]
Thank goodness for Korin!
We are well aware of
the restorative properties
of the Senzu Bean Yes,
the bean's magic has begun
to heal your body just as
it healed your friend's,
but we will not allow you
the time to recover.
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[GOKU grunts]
--[ANDROID 19] Ha-ha!
--[GOKU grunts]
[blows landing,
GOKU grunts]
[ANDROID 19] Ha-haa...
[GOKU grunts]
--[ALL gasping]
--[KRILLIN] Oh man! Goku!
The Senzu Bean
isn't working!
What do you mean?!
The Senzu Beans have
always worked for us before!
No! That's got to
be it! I'm positive!
He needs to have the antidote
but we have to go back home
to get it! It's the only way!
[PICCOLO] Huh?!
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[GOKU grunts]
[blows landing,
ANDROID 19 laughing]
[GOKU grunts]
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
Oh, no! Dad!
He changed back!
Goku changed!
He's not a Super Saiyan anymore!
Man! That's not good!
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[ANDROID 19] Mmm!
Yes! Perfect!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU shouts]
[ANDROID 19] Hmm...?
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[PICCOLO gasps]
That's it, you guys!
Goku's in trouble!
Let's move in!
[ANDROID 20] You will
stay where you are!
That is, of course,
unless any of you are
foolish enough to believe
that you can get past me.
[ALL growl]
Just as I thought.
Think again.
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN] Oh, no! Piccolo!
[GOHAN] Please be okay!
What's your deal?! Why do
you hurt people, huh?!
Do not test my
patience, human. Fool.
Have you not learned
from Piccolo's mistake?
[ANDROID 19 sighs]
[GOKU rasps]
We need to do something,
you guys! Look!
He's running out of time!
[TIEN growls]
[GOKU rasps,
ANDROID 19 giggles]
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[GOKU yells]
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[ANDROID 20] Huh?!
[GOHAN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[VEGETA] Nobody kills
Kakarot while I'm around!
Destiny has reserved
that pleasure for me!
[ANDROID 19] Mmm?
[ANDROID 19 growls]
Wow! Vegeta!
Vegeta...
That's who it was!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Piccolo, you're okay!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
I admit, the move I
made wasn't very smart,
but I wanted to
help Goku out!
And then, boom!
Vegeta got in my way!
It wasn't the android?!
The android did got a shot in,
but only after
Vegeta interfered!
You're pitiful, Kakarot.
You were warned
about the heart virus!
You should have known that
turning into a Super Saiyan
could only make it worse!
[GOKU grunts]
[VEGETA] Really, Kakarot!
You're far too forgiving
to be a great warrior!
I'll finish these androids,
but then, you're next!
Got it?!
[GOKU groans]
--[VEGETA] Good.
--[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU groans]
Daddy, no! Hold on,
Dad! Please! Hold on!
[TIEN] He's holding
on by a thread!
[GOHAN] He's unconscious,
but he's still breathing!
[VEGETA] One of you needs to
take Kakarot home right now
and give him the antidote!
He's running out of time!
[GOHAN] C'mon, Dad! You're
going to be alright! I promise!
I'm taking you home!
Please! Let me!
They need you, kid!
Sad to say, but I'd
just be in the way here!
Hey, you'd better take
a swig of that antidote, too!
If the disease is viral,
there's a good chance
you could get it as well!
[YAMCHA] Right! Thanks, Piccolo!
I'm counting on you,
Yamcha! Take care!
Better get a move on.
Right! We'll be okay!
Just stay alive
until we get back!
[YAMCHA] Alright,
Goku! Let's do it!
[KRILLIN] Hurry back,
Goku! We need you!
[ANDROID 19 growls]
Let them go!
They pose us no threat!
[ANDROID 19] Hmph!
[ANDROID 20]
You have done well, 19.
It is obvious that Goku
is no match for us.
We can finish him at the
moment of our choosing.
Until then, we will
entertain ourselves
by destroying all of
his pitiful "friends."
[YAJIROBE] Oooh!
[YAJIROBE blows raspberry]
[BABY TRUNKS laughs]
[YAJIROBE chuckles]
[YAJIROBE]
You like that, don't you?
Heh, heh, heh...
You little stinker.
[BULMA] I had no idea
you were so good
with kids, Yajirobe!
--[YAJIROBE] Huh?
--Yeah!
Usually he starts crying
when other people hold him.
[YAJIROBE] So you like
Uncle Yajirobe, huh?
Well, I like you, too!
Yes, I do! Yes, I do!
--Tickle tickle!
--[BABY TRUNKS laughs]
Haaah!
[YAJIROBE grunts]
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
You gave him a
sour face! Poor boy!
He got his feelings hurt!
[YAJIROBE] Hey! I'm the
one who got all wet!
[BULMA] There, there!
It's okay! He didn't mean it!
Oh, no! We're out
of diapers, Trunks!
I don't have anything
dry to put you in!
Oh, wait! Yajirobe
has something!
[BULMA giggles]
[YAJIROBE] Hmm.
[BULMA] Thank you, Yajirobe,
you're so sweet! Come 'ere, boy!
[BABY TRUNKS whimpers]
There! That's better! Yeah!
Thanks to our Yajirobe!
He always comes through
for you in a pinch!
Eh, that's true.
Yeah. Right...
[BULMA] Now, let's go see Daddy!
What?! No way!
Yes way! Why not?
Vegeta wouldn't let
anything happen
to his little boy.
We'll be just fine.
No, we won't!
We'll be... dead!
[BULMA] Hey! Come on, man!
Where's your sense
of adventure?
Let's do it!
Please? Come on!
And besides... Trunks
needs you! Don't you boy?
[YAJIROBE groans]
[YAJIROBE] Why me?!
Come on and get in!
Alright, but
you listen here.
One peek, and then
we're out of there!
Alright, fine! Don't be rude!
Get in and let's go!
[BULMA growls]
Huh?
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
Here we go!
[YAJIROBE] You're crazy! Whoa!
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[ANDROID 20] Yes. This is
going to be very enjoyable.
[ANDROID 20] Hmm...
Gohan! I think it
might be a wise idea
for us to get out of here.
[GOHAN] Huh?
[TIEN] Huh?
[KRILLIN] Remember what that
guy from the future told Goku
about us?! That all of us
except you are going to perish
in a battle against
the androids!
Well, why should we
let that happen?!
It doesn't make sense!
Why don't we get the
heck out of here?!
There are some
minor differences,
but the stage does
seem set for us to die!
Yeah, but If we
leave right now,
those two will probably
go on a killing spree
like they did in that town! Are
you sure that's what you want!
Do you really want to take off?
[KRILLIN] Not for good!
Just until Goku's better!
There's a chance
that it might not happen
like that guy said it would!
There are
some differences.
Goku being alive
is a major one!
So I say we act
as if we never
heard that guy's
prophecy before.
[KRILLIN growls]
[thinking] These
guys are iron-clad!
It's hard to keep pace
with them sometimes!
I'm only human! I want to live!
I will finish Vegeta now. Yes.
[ANDROID 20] You are being
very greedy today, 19.
You have already absorbed
enough energy from Goku
to increase your power,
have you not?
[ANDROID 20] Very well.
You finish Vegeta,
but the rest are mine.
Do you understand?
Hmm... Ha!
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
I was waching your
battle with Kakarot,
so I've seen your energy
absorbing technique.
Oh well, if I can't
blast you away,
I'll have to pound you
to a pulp, that's all!
You know some
of my moves,
but I know all of
your moves, Vegeta!
Oh, yes, Doctor Gero
studied you very thoroughly!
[VEGETA] Oh, is that a fact?
Then why were you so surprised
when Kakarot turned
into a Super Saiyan?
I'll tell you why,
because your database
doesn't cover the
battles we had in space!
Your bonehead creator
picked a fine chapter
to omit from your memory banks!
Oh?
That's right my friend!
Let me ask you,
does a machine like yourself
ever experience fear?
[VEGETA grunts]
[grunting continues]
[VEGETA growls]
[KRILLIN] You've got to be
kidding me! I don't believe it!
[GOHAN gasps]
[ANDROID 19 gasps]
Not him, too!
[VEGETA yells]
[yelling continues]
Whoa! You know who joined
the Super Saiyan Club!
He is on our side, isn't he?!
Whoa! I'm confused! I thought
you had to be like Goku
to be one!
Goku's so calm and
detached and purehearted,
but obviously those
aren't prerequisites!
[VEGETA] Afraid not!
There's more than one way
to reach the goal!
Yes! To each his own!
[VEGETA] My motivation was
very different than Kakarot's!
My motivation was
to be the best!
To be the greatest Saiyan
alive as I always had been!
Until Kakarot came into
the picture that is!
[VEGETA] Kakarot's success
was like a demon in my head!
How could he be a
Super Saiyan when I,
the Prince of all
Saiyans, could not!
[VEGETA] The intensity of
my training was maddening!
At four-hundred and
fifty times normal gravity,
a basic training game became a
desperate struggle for survival!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] Even the simplest
moves required every ounce
of will power I had!
[VEGETA] I wasn't sure how
long I could sustain the effort
without breaking in two!
It seemed like the only thing
holding my body together
was my one desire:
to be better than Kakarot!
[VEGETA] At times I thought
I was losing my mind!
Why couldn't I obtain
what Kakarot had obtained?!
It didn't make sense!
It was infuriating
and it was my fury
that kept me alive!
[VEGETA] I decided
to continue my training
in the solitude of space,
where I would be unhindered
by the distractions
of the Earth.
And when a violent electrical
storm erupted in the skies
of the planet I was on,
I welcomed it!
It seemed fitting... Like it
was an outward manifestation
of the storm that
was raging inside of me!
[VEGETA] Then the meteors
started coming down!
But I was determined to
survive and to protect
my ship from destruction!
It was my only way out!
My only way off of that
nightmarish heap of rubble!
[VEGETA] I thought I had
everything under control.
But then, the mother of all
meteors seemed to appear
out of nowhere to claim
my ship and my life!
[VEGETA screams]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] Normally it would
have been child's play
to blow up that rock!
But after training at
four-hundred and fifty times
normal gravity for so long, it
took everything I had, and more!
[VEGETA screams]
Ka... karot!
Then something just snapped,
something inside of me!
No! No more! That's it!
I don't care!
[VEGETA] I didn't care
anymore! I didn't care
about being
better than Kakarot,
I didn't care about
being a Super Saiyan,
I didn't care if I lived!
I didn't care about anything!
And then... it happened!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] Yes,
that's how it happened!
That's how I
became a Super Saiyan!
The sleeper has awakened!
I am the prince of all
Saiyans once again!
Enough of this
nonsense, fool.
You may have become
a Super Saiyan,
but your new found powers
are still no match for us.
Please demonstrate, 19!
[GOHAN] Huh?!
--Uh?
--Hm?
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[NARRATOR] As the radically
powerful Android 19
charges down the war-path,
Vegeta stands firm
and confident in his newfound
power. But is it enough?
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!