[ZARBON roars]
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z...
Vegeta and Zarbon
went head-to-head
in a no-holds-barred
battle to the finish,
where Vegeta proved
once and for all
that he had
the upper hand...
[VEGETA] Raah!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Krillin, realizing
that he was no match for Vegeta,
gave up the Dragon Ball
given to him by Guru...
[VEGETA] The last Dragon Ball
is finally in my possession!
Now, all that remains is
calling forth the Dragon!
Then I'll have my wish for
immortality and become the
Supreme Ruler of the Universe!
And Frieza will die!
[VEGETA laughs]
[thinking] I don't
think so, Vegeta...
You'll never get
to make that wish...
[NARRATOR] That's because Gohan
has recovered the
last Dragon Ball,
but will he make it back
before Vegeta finds him?
Find out today!
[BULMA] How could you hand
it over so easily, Krillin?
You heard him!
He said that's
the last one!
And now he's going
to summon the dragon
and make his wish, so it
looks like we're doomed...
[KRILLIN] He would have killed
us for that Dragon Ball...
And then he would've taken
it from us anyway...
At least this way,
we managed to stay alive.
But even with
that ball,
he still can't
make his wish yet...
Uh?
Gohan didn't know it,
but he stopped him.
Didn't you say that he
left here to go after
a Dragon Ball you
saw on the radar?
One that had
been left behind?
[BULLMA gasps]
You're right, Krillin!
You've got it!
Gohan has just one
of the Dragon Balls,
then Vegeta can't
make his wish!
I knew that little guy
would come through for us!
Let's just hope that he
doesn't run into Vegeta.
[quietly whimpering]
Zarbon's late...
Ah! Right!
I tire of waiting... He
should have been back by now.
Either Vegeta
has defeated him...
Or, he has failed
in his mission
and run away
to escape me...
I knew it! I should
have dispatched
the Ginyu Force
from the very beginning!
Ah! Lord Frieza!
You'll be pleased to know,
the Ginyu Force has been
notified of your command
and are making preparations
for immediate departure!
I'm expecting
confirmation any minute now!
There, you see?
Now that's professionalism.
[FRIEZA giggles]
Oh, and Namole?
Ah?
I'm afraid with the
Ginyu Force coming,
you will no longer
be needed. Ever.
Ah!
[NAMOLE screams]
[SOLDIERS whimpering]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[DISPATCHER]
Attention! Attention!
All members of
the Ginyu Force!
This is a Red Alert! I repeat!
This is a Red Alert!
[DISPATCHER] Report to your
space pods immediately!
This is not a drill!
Repeat! This is not a drill!
Stand by for
launch sequence!
[DISPATCHER] Begin launch
sequence! T-minus 30!
Launch in
T-minus 25!
In T-minus 20
and counting...
T-minus 15...
T-minus 10...
T-minus 5...
T-minus zero! Countdown
complete. Lift off!
There they go off
to Planet Namek.
I'd hate to be the guys
that have to take them on.
[YAMCHA grunting]
What's going on?!
Huh?
I sense a powerful force is
headed for Planet Namek...
Y'mean Goku?
[KING KAI] No, there are
5 of them... Evil...
[KING KAI gasps]
It's the
Ginyu Force!
[PICCOLO gasps]
It's... The
Gin-who-what?
They're a-a highly trained and
highly secret assault team.
[KING KAI]
Across the universe,
wars have erupted
without warning.
Cities and civilizations
have been demolished,
planets left in ruin...
All with no clear idea
as to how or why such
horrors ever began.
But I know who
is responsible.
A secret elite army
called the Ginyu Force.
The private
army of Frieza!
Well, now that we've been
through your training,
the only force they're
gonna be is forced back home!
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
Nice one, Yamcha!
[YAMCHA] Yeah... yeah,
I just made that up!
[ALL laughing]
Hey, King Kai!
Don't you get it?
Uh... Hey, uh, King Kai?
[thinking]
This isn't good...
The soldiers in the
Ginyu Force are powerful.
Just one of them alone is 5
times more powerful than Goku!
No one can stop
them. No one!
[GOKU yelling]
[grunting]
Wow, this working out
in 100 times gravity
is starting
to pay off!
[GOKU] Well, no
time to waste!
[GOKU yelling]
[GOHAN gasps]
Something's
headed this way!
It's powerful...
[GOHAN] Vegeta!
Oh, no!
[VEGETA gasps]
I'm sensing someone
else, just up ahead.
[thinking] I've got to
try to hide my power level!
Where are you?
Come out!
[VEGETA] I can't
sense your power level,
but I know you're down there.
[thinking] Please!
Just go away! Leave!
[VEGETA] Whoever you are,
show yourself!
You can't hide
forever...
If you don't
come out,
I'll start blasting this
entire area until I find you!
[thinking]
What am I gonna do?
[VEGETA] Come out!
Last chance!
[thinking]
I've got no choice...
I'm going to have to show
myself and face him...
Gohan, you're not strong
enough to defeat Vegeta!
[thinking] No matter
what happens,
I've got to protect
this Dragon Ball!
[VEGETA] Well, have
it your way then.
One way or another,
I will find you!
[VEGETA growling]
[GOHAN gasps]
[growling continues]
Prepare to die!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN]
Wait! Wait!
[thinking] I sure
hope it's safe here.
Stop! Here I am!
Ah... The son of Kakarot...
The son
of Kakarot...
Well. I should have
known it was you.
We meet again!
[VEGETA] I just met
with your friends.
I suspected you
might be close by.
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] A Dragon Ball!
Where did you
get that from?!
It was a gift from the
bald-headed one.
And that bratty girl
that was with him.
[GOHAN] What did you
do to them?! Huh?
Did you hurt them?!
Answer me!
[VEGETA] Actually I
never even touched them,
but if you want, I could easily
be talked into going back!
[GOHAN gasps]
You see, boy,
because I now possess
all of the Dragon Balls,
I was, as you
say, "merciful".
He thinks he
has all of them...
[GOHAN screams]
[VEGETA] Tell me, what's
that thing in your hand?
It's just a watch!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] With all the scientific
technology on your planet,
you're trying to tell me that
that huge device is a watch?
It's an
antique watch!
Anyway... Is your father
on this planet as well?
No, he's not! I don't
know where my dad is.
I haven't seen him in
a very long time.
Hmph.
Such neglect...
Awww...
Too bad.
Because, you see...
We are the last
of the Saiyans.
That means we have to
look out for one another.
Understand?
It's like... like the
three of us are brothers.
[VEGETA] Hrrgh!
Haaugh...
[GOHAN groaning]
Not too bright,
are you boy?
You're even a bigger
fool than your father.
And that's
saying a lot!
[groaning continues]
Go home. Go cry
in the arms
of your mother,
little Saiyan.
This is no place for
a sniveling baby!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Bye.
[GOHAN whimpering]
The Dragon Ball...
He... he...
He never found the
other Dragon Ball!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN chuckles]
[KRILLIN growls frustratedly]
Gohan!
Krillin!
I've packed everything
back into a capsule!
Any sign of
Gohan yet?
No sign of anything!
I'm beginning to think
that something terrible
has happened to him!
After seeing Vegeta
take out that monster,
I don't want to think about
what he could do to Gohan...
Come on, Gohan. Hurry!
We've got to get out of
here! Gohan! Please!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Hey! Krillin!
Gohan!
[GOHAN] You guys!
Look what I found!
Yes!
Way to go, Gohan!
You did it, kid!
[GOHAN laughs]
Uh, Gohan,
we'll have to save
the celebrating
until later,
because right now we
gotta to get outta here!
[GOHAN] Yeah, I know. Vegeta
told me that he'd been here.
Uhh...
I was able to hide the
Dragon Ball from him!
He never even
knew I had it!
No way!
Boy, were we lucky!
Krillin! Gohan!
Move it or loose it!
--Okay...
--[KRILLIN] Oh, right!
[VEGETA laughs]
This is it! The last
Dragon Ball is right here.
And all I have to do is
swim down there and get it.
[thinking] In mere
moments I will possess
all of the
Dragon Balls,
and then the universe
will be mine!
No one, not even Frieza,
will be able to stop me...
[thinking] Hmm...
That's strange...
It's got to be around
here somewhere...
[thinking] Where is it?
[VEGETA thinking]
Where is that damn ball?!
[thinking] NO!
[VEGETA] It was that boy!
I sensed he was
hiding something from me!
He has the Dragon Ball! That
little brat stole it from me!
But how did
he get it?!
It's just a watch!
[thinking]
That was no watch!
It was some kind of
Dragon Ball locator!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yelling]
When I find you,
I'll kill you! You're dead!
I swear it!
You are dead!
Where are you, boy?!
I want that Dragon Ball!
[VEGETA] NOOOO!
[VEGETA growling]
Where is he?!
[VEGETA] They're hiding.
I can't sense their energy.
But I'll find them...
The instant they make their
next move, I'll find them!
No one makes a
fool out of me!
I swear they'll regret the
day they were ever born!
They won't leave
here without trying
to get the other
Dragon Balls,
and when that time
inevitably comes
they will have to
deal with me...
[VEGETA chuckles]
We're safe now. Vegeta will
never find us down here.
Why would anyone look for
us in such a horrible place?
Well, uh, look on the
bright side, Bulma.
At least this way you're not
stuck in a cave anymore.
Krillin's right, we just gotta
be positive, that's all!
You want positive?
Alright!
I am positive that
we have no food,
or water or even a
bathroom for that matter!
How's that
for positive?
Well?
Hey, I got an
idea, Bulma!
Why don't you wait
here while Gohan and I
visit Guru and get him to
awaken Gohan's hidden powers.
To... to do what?
I will not be left out
here all by myself, okay?
You gotta
trust me.
First of all, we'll be
back before you know it!
And second,
when we do return,
Vegeta won't stand a
chance against me and Gohan!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[NARRATOR] The special assault
team known as the Ginyu Force
has answered
Frieza's call
and is on its way
to Planet Namek.
Once these
mercenaries arrive,
Frieza will be
unstoppable...
But they're not the only
ones headed for Namek...
Goku is also en-route
to the planet,
training hard and pushing his
strength further and further...
And while Vegeta searches in
vain for the Dragon Balls,
Krillin is taking
Gohan to meet Guru,
who will unlock the secret
powers lying within him...
It's a race
against time,
but who will win,
and who will be too late?
The fate of our heroes
hangs in the balance...
Don't miss the next
action-packed episode of
Dragon Ball Z!