[VEGETA]
I can't give up!
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta completed his recovery
and sped away to Planet Namek,
where he learned the evil
Frieza and his henchmen
were already searching
for the magic Dragon Balls
and the secret
to immortality.
Meanwhile, Bulma and
the gang found themselves
at the mercy of
Raiti and Zaacro,
as they began to
discover that things
were not what
they seemed!
It appears our heroes have been
caught in a web of deceit,
and this unexpected
snag in their search
for the Namekian Dragon Balls
could cost them dearly...
With Vegeta on
his way to Namek,
our heroes have
no time to lose!
Can they escape these
mysterious aliens? Stay tuned!
[GOHAN grunting]
Hang in there!
[GOHAN shouts]
[RAITI and ZAACRO laugh]
Don't worry, they're
night feeders,
so they won't
eat you now.
They'll just hold
you there 'til dark,
giving us
time to escape.
[BULMA] Hold on,
I'm confused.
The last I remember,
I was on Planet Namek.
Well, welcome to the
armpit of the universe.
We've become quite
familiar with it
since our ship
crashed here.
And believe me,
what you see around you
is as good
as it gets.
But just when we
had given up hope
of ever getting off
this smoldering rock,
along you came
to save the day,
bringing us a ship
that we could steal
and use for
our escape.
[ZAACRO] We planned to leave
with your ship that night,
but the conditions
weren't right,
so we bid our time
until they were.
We were simply, how do
you say, killing time.
We decided that we'd have a
little fun on your behalf
while we
were waiting,
and stumbled across
something better
than we could
have ever imagined.
[BULMA] But, this isn't
making any sense!
[ZAACRO] We brought you
three back to our home here.
A building culled from the
parts of our wrecked ship
and fashioned into a
makeshift laboratory.
[ZAACRO] I scanned you
and uncovered
some very
interesting information
about the Dragon Balls
you were searching for
and their location
on Planet Namek.
[RAITI and ZAACRO chuckling]
[BULMA] B-But then,
how did you...
I still don't
understand at all!
[ZAACRO] It was all
just an illusion.
[BULMA] Is this how you
guys get your kicks? Is it?!
[RAITI] You have to admit
it was pretty exciting.
[KRILLIN] You gotta
be kidding me!
You're not
taking our ship.
Is that right?
And what are you
going to do about it?
Your friends seem to be
all tied up at the moment.
[ZAACRO] But we don't really
have a taste for violence.
So let us leave and
we'll go peacefully.
We could have
taken your lives
before we took your
ship, but we didn't.
Instead we gave
you a little dream
to keep your attention
until we could sneak away.
You jerk.
Now, the time is right
for us to make our escape.
Soon an opening
will form,
allowing a ship
to leave the planet.
Hey! Gimme that back!
You won't be
needing it anymore.
And I think we'll stop and
pick up the Dragon Balls
ourselves on
our way home.
And now you'll be left
stranded on this rock
waiting for someone
to happen by
and take you away
from this desolation.
[BULMA] You won't
get away with this!
You hear me?!
Don't just stand
there shouting!
Run after
them, hurry!
What exactly do you
expect me to do about it?!
I don't know!
But do something!
So, please tell me that you
know how to fly this thing.
Piece of cake.
It's all voice activated.
All I have to do is say
the word and we're off.
[ZAACRO]
Then do it already!
[RAITI] Here goes. Open up
and take us to Planet Namek!
[ZAACRO] Is that it?
[RAITI] I don't know!
Maybe it needs a secret word.
[thinking] They don't even
know how to open the door!
So much for
their escape plan.
[growling]
[KRILLIN grunting]
How you doing, Gohan?
[GOHAN]
I... can't get loose!
No! Krillin!
I'm coming.
[GOHAN yelling]
[thinking]
It's working!
Haah!
[thinking] I'm almost
there, Krillin.
Yeah!
Huh?
[RAITI] I tried that already!
[ZAACRO] Well, there's gotta be
some way to get into this ship.
[ZAACRO] Hurry, or
we'll miss our chance
to get out
of this hole!
[RAITI] I'll go get the girl and
make her tell us how to work it.
Oh, no! Gotta hide!
[BULMA sighs]
[screams]
[BOTH] Huh?
[BULMA laughing]
All right!
Yahoo!
[RAITI]
Now, open the door.
[ZAACRO] We don't have
any time to waste.
If this window of
opportunity closes
we won't be able to leave
again for another year.
But can't we work
something out?
Maybe I could drop
you off somewhere else.
But it'll take fifty years
to reach our home planet.
You sure you're
up for that?
Fifty years?!
[ZAACRO] Now, hurry!
I guess I have
no choice...
[BULMA clears throat]
[BULMA] Piccolo!
Superb!
Told you! All it needed
was the right password.
[BULMA shouts]
[BULMA whimpering]
Good luck. And besides,
it's really not bad here.
You'll have
lots of fun.
Oh, and remember,
don't drink the water,
and don't go out
alone after dark.
Do that,
you'll be fine.
[BOTH laughing]
[GOHAN] Piccolo!
[laughing continues]
[BOTH] Huh?
[RAITI] Impossible!
Whew... You made it.
We're heroes, that's
what we do, right?
[GOHAN growling]
Well, then...
Show us what you got.
[GOHAN and KRILLIN yelling]
That was a lot easier
than I expected.
Yeah.
[RAITI] We told you we didn't
have a taste for violence.
We weren't joking,
you know.
[BULMA] Oh no!
Looks like the
fog's clearing up.
If we don't
leave now,
then we won't be able
to for another year!
[BULMA] Piccolo.
Later fellas!
Without you we would've never
known how to escape from here.
I guess we owe you one, then!
Thanks guys! Bye!
Hey Bulma, are you sure
you know what you're doing?
Hang in there, Krillin.
Looks like we're in
for a bumpy ride.
I don't know if
we can make it.
We have to try.
Here we go!
[BULMA] We made it.
Now to make up for
all that lost time.
We're on to
Planet Namek,
and I'm gonna give
her all she's got.
We need to get
there in a hurry.
So what do we do now,
genius? Any bright ideas?
No, I'm pretty much
fresh out of bright ideas.
[BOTH sigh]
[BOTH] We'll never
get off this rock...
[VEGETA thinking]
Frieza... Ha!
He'll bow to me once I've
recovered the Dragon Balls.
And then no one will
stand in my way!
[CHICHI humming]
[CHICHI]
I was thinking, Goku...
What is it, ChiChi?
Our little boy's been gone
for almost a month now.
Yeah, and...?
[CHICHI] And I think I forgot
to pack his toenail clippers.
I packed the
fingernail ones,
but they just don't work
for toes, you know.
[GOKU] I'm sure he'll make
do with what he's got.
Sheesh.
[GOKU yelling]
[chuckling]
[GOKU stuttering]
[laughing]
Nice day,
isn't it, doctor?
[BULMA] I can't believe it!
I thought we'd never make it.
Aah, beautiful!
Yeah, I've never seen
anything else like it.
And this time it's
the real Planet Namek.
I just got confirmation
from the computer system.
[GOHAN] We're here, and
only four days off schedule.
Yeah, well, our little
detour notwithstanding...
The shortcut those kids
told us about was right on!
Take us down, Bulma.
What are we waiting for?
You two! Now sit down
and put on your seat belts.
We're entering
an atmosphere,
not taking a ride
around the block.
So, strap in, and
hope for the best.
[grunting]
[KRILLIN shouting]
[BULMA]
A perfect landing!
Someone needs to
compliment me on my skills,
'cause I
sure got 'em!
[ALL laughing]
[BULMA] Now, I'll just use this
atmospheric sensor
I built back
on Earth.
It'll tell us whether
or not there's enough
breathable oxygen on
the planet's surface
for us to walk
around freely.
Or if we need
to wear suits.
I'm betting we'll
need those suits.
They'll work fine
for a short time.
After that, the air
tanks will deplete and...
Huh?
This place, you know,
except for the sky,
it doesn't really look all
that different from Earth...
Yeah, it does sorta
look like home.
But it's way
too quiet.
It kind of gives me
the creeps, you know?
I guess so.
What do you think you're
doing just walking around
before I say it's okay?!
You could have died!
What if you had walked outside
and there would've
been no oxygen?!
Well, freak out,
why don't you?
You're lucky. So from now on,
nobody moves until I say so.
I've picked up four
Dragon Balls already!
And they're
close, too...
[BULMA yelps]
What are
you doing?
Heh... I just
wanted to check
and make sure I wasn't
dreaming, you know?
Pinch yourself!
It's real.
[BULMA laughing]
Uh!
[BULMA and KRILLIN
laughing]
Hey, I'm sensing
something over there...
[laughing continues]
[BOTH] Huh?
Where?
[GOHAN] It's near,
and strong.
I feel it
too, Gohan.
And I don't like
it one bit.
You're worrying
yourselves over nothing.
Piccolo had a powerful
energy level,
it's only natural that his
fellow people would as well.
You're probably just sensing
one of Piccolo's relatives
while he's sitting at
his house having dinner.
But...
This energy's different,
it feels wrong.
[BULMA] Don't be silly!
The only people around here
are the local Namekians,
and they're peaceful.
They're no
threat to you.
Now, come on.
The Dragon Balls are this way.
If we get those we're
over half way there.
So let's go meet some locals
and collect some Dragon Balls.
Okay. You're, uh,
probably right.
We got ourselves
worked up over nothing.
Heh, heh! I'm kind of
embarrassed about it, actually.
[KRILLIN laughing]
[BOTH] Hmm?
Huh?
Wh-What kind of
ship is that?
[KRILLIN] It looks
like a Saiyan ship!
Now, I'm scared!
That's just great!
[BULMA] This can't
be happening!
It's just
a dream!
[KRILLIN] Gohan! Mask your
energy or he'll sense you.
Uh, right!
It's Vegeta!
It's gotta be.
Rrrgh...
Raagh!
[BULMA] Did you...
just say... Vegeta?
And he must be here
for the Dragon Balls.
What do we do? We can't
possibly fight Vegeta!
And if he gets the Dragon
Balls before us, we're doomed!
[KRILLIN] There's no
way we're gonna let him
get to them
before we do...
Bulma, you gotta leave now.
Go back to Earth alone.
We'll take care
of things here.
Just leave us your
Radar, and Gohan and I
will collect
the Dragon Balls.
But...
It's okay.
Don't worry about us.
I don't think we'll
get into any trouble...
We know what
we're doing.
Yeah!
[BULMA] I understand.
Sure, I'll leave you guys
here and go back to Earth,
but I'm coming
back with Goku.
But I think that you
guys should know,
that'll take
two months.
But what's two months,
anyways?! Just 60 days!
One thousand four
hundred and forty hours!
Eighty-six thousand four
hundred minutes!
Five million, one hundred
eighty-four thousand seconds...
right?!
Uh... yeah, it's only
two months.
[BOTH chuckling sheepishly]
It's time...
Time to remove the only
obstacle standing in my way.
Once the Dragon Balls
are in my possession,
all the power of
eternal life will be mine.
And then no one will
be able to stop me.
Not even the
mighty Frieza.
I'm already picking
up his power level.
So, he's near.
I'm coming for you, Frieza.
I sure hope you're ready.
[ROSHI] What?
What did you say?
Okay, got that...
Yes, go on...
[BULMA] You sure
you understand?
Tell Goku.
But whatever you do,
don't tell ChiChi.
She'll freak!
So, one more time.
Repeat it back to me.
[engine roaring in distance]
Okay, yeah... Good...
[engine roaring getting louder]
Keep going... Uh-huh.
No, you got that
part backwards!
Right! Did you
get all that?!
You better
have, old man!
What's going on?
Did I miss something?
[laughing sheepishly]
Uh... What?
[BULMA squealing]
Wah! W-Was that
Vegeta's ship again?
No, that's a
different ship this time.
For you,
Lord Frieza.
[FRIEZA] Very good.
Just three more
to go, now.
[FRIEZA laughing]
[laughing]
[NARRATOR]
What's this?
The evil tyrant Frieza and his
ruthless henchmen have already
gathered four of the seven
Namekian Dragon Balls!
And it seems there is nothing
to stand in the villain's way
of collecting the rest...
Even the mighty Vegeta,
with all of his
Saiyan strength,
is afraid to face
this foe head on!
Gohan and Krillin have
a monumental task
set before them.
Even if they can get to
the remaining Dragon Balls
before Frieza
or Vegeta,
they'll have to stay
alive for two months
before Bulma and
Goku can return!
The race is on...
And the fate of Planet Namek
hangs in the balance...
Next time, on
Dragon Ball Z!