[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell was about to absorb
Android 17 into his being
when Android 16
lodged a silent complaint.
Like a raging bull,
the strong, silent Android
charged into battle
and attacked Cell
with all he had.
It was soon evident
that Android 16
was every bit as strong as Cell.
Leaving nothing to chance,
the giant Android proceeded
to rip off Cell's tail,
ensuring that the
greedy monster could never
absorb another life
into his being again!
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[CELL screams]
[NARRATOR] But
Cell had other plans,
and he would not be deterred
from completing his
deadly evolution so easily.
A little tail regeneration,
and he was back in business.
[ANDROID 16] Hmm?
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Since some
of Piccolo's cells
comprise my cellular structure,
I, too, have the ability
to regenerate my body!
[NARRATOR]
The epic battle continues...
...today on Dragon Ball Z!
[thinking]
Full regeneration?
How can you beat a
creature like that?!
[thinking] He's hideous.
I could never be a part of that!
[thinking]
He's just too much...
[CELL]
A valiant effort, my friend,
but just a minor
inconvenience to me.
[CELL chuckles]
I thought I had the
solution, but I did not.
You are bound to have a
weak point somewhere, though!
Really now? We'll see.
This time I'll
rip off your head!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL]
You'll have to catch me first!
[CELL growls]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
[CELL]
So much for that strategy...
Now, do you have
any other tricks,
or can I get
on with my work?
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
Aaahhh...
[CELL growls]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[CELL yells]
[grunting]
[ANDROID 16 grunts,
CELL screams]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[yelling]
[thinking]
16's... stronger!
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
Wow, 16, you're doing it!
[thinking]
This guy is too much!
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
Blasters fire! Aaahh!
[TIEN stammers]
[KRILLIN] Huh...?
[KRILLIN gasps]
[thinking] Holy cow!
Look at those fireworks!
Those guys are going
all out over there!
[thinking] Wait a sec... I can
feel Tien's energy signal!
[thinking] Oh, great!
What's he doing over there?
So much for the plan!
Aw, man! Now what?
I can't go over there now.
Not without the remote.
Sorry, Tien.
I've got to find Bulma first!
[GOKU]
Wow! That's strange!
Cell's energy signal
just took a nose-dive!
Yeah, I felt it,
too, Dad. Is he losing?
[GOKU] It doesn't seem
possible, but somebody seems
to have the upper
hand on him right now.
Now, if they could just
hold on a little longer!
He's great!
[ANDROID 17]
Incredible...
16 beat Cell!
16...
[ANDROID 16]
Why are you still here?!
I told you to leave this place!
Hey, you squashed the bug. What
is there to be afraid of now?
That attack was not
enough to finish Cell!
It is imperative you run
from this place immediately!
You, too, 17!
Don't give Cell the
chance to absorb you!
Don't worry.
I think you've taken the wind
out of that freak's sails.
You're obviously
stronger than he is!
And with us at your side...
no one can even
touch our little gang!
I'm telling you 16, you are
truly state of the art!
I'll admit I was
scared there for a second,
but now, heh, now I know...
Soon we'll have the whole
world as our playground.
Just the three of us,
doing anything we want.
[TIEN gasps]
[TIEN] 17! Look out!
He's behind you!
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[CELL shrieks]
[ANDROID 16 gasps]
You should've
listened to your friend!
[ANDROID 17 muffled]
No! Let go!
[muffled yelling]
Nooo!
[CELL laughs]
[CELL screams]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
It's... horrible!
[CELL growls]
[ANDROID 17 screams]
[CELL yells]
[yelling continues]
[CELL roars]
[ANDROID 16 yells]
[CELL snarling]
[snarling continues]
[ANDROID 16]
18! Come on!
We cannot allow him
to absorb you too!
You had better
get out of here now!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] Whoa!
This isn't good!
It feels like Cell's power level
just went through the roof!
[GOHAN]
Yeah...
It's what we feared.
Cell must have gotten one
of the androids, Gohan.
It's the only explanation!
[CELL] Ahh, yes! This is much
nicer! How exhilarating!
[TIEN thinking] Oh my gosh...
We should've stopped him.
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] Yes, I could get used
to this! I've waited so long...
He wants you, 18!
We must go!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Ah-ahh...
No! He is as strong as I feared!
[TIEN thinking]
Great!
It looks like I might have to
get my feet wet after all...
You can't escape me. It's over.
You had a small window of
opportunity to defeat me,
but now it's too late!
[TIEN thinking] Okay, Tien...
What would Goku do
if he were here?
[thinking] He'd do
everything he could
to keep that Android
away from Cell!
Even die!
Ah, a new look! Much more
comely than the last!
Merging with 18
should have a similar effect.
[ANDROID 16 yells]
Huh?
Huh?!
[CELL chuckles]
[ANDROID 16 gasps]
[ANDROID 18]
16! No! Look out!
[ANDROID 16 yells]
So, Android 18,
it's your turn. Come here.
[ANDROID 18] I'm not listening
to anything you say.
Look what you've done!
You're a monster!
Ahh! Feisty.
[ANDROID 18] Why don't
you just go back
to wherever you came from?
[CELL] I'm on the verge
of becoming a god,
what do you think?
I'll leave...
My dear android,
when will you understand
that you belong to me?
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[CELL]
Well, shall we get started?
Just relax.
You know the routine.
[ANDROID 18] Stay where
you are. I'm warning you.
One step closer
and I'll detonate!
Huh?!
Extinguish yourself?
You wouldn't dare!
Oh, no? Just try me.
Anything's better
than merging with you.
I'm not a creature like you are.
We're completely different.
How can I be a part of you?
[CELL] I think I know someone
who can answer that for you.
[ANDROID 17 (CELL)]
Hey, 18, what's up? Don't worry.
It's me, 17.
Huh?
What's the deal?
You're scared, huh?
Don't worry, look. I'm fine.
I know that it's hard
to understand, but we were
meant to be together
as part of Cell.
Once you join us,
it will all become clear.
Join you? Are you sure?
[ANDROID 17 (CELL)] 18! Would I
ever do anything to hurt you?
Don't listen to him!
That's not 17!
Cell is using
his voice to trick you!
[CELL]
Be quiet, you fool!
You only have half a brain left!
You have no idea
what you're talking about!
Please continue, 17.
You do whatever you want, 18...
But doesn't it make
sense to do as Dr. Gero
intended and become one
ultimate being above all others?
It's what we were made for!
There is no higher
purpose for us!
I'm not buying it!
That's not 17!
17 loved
the person he was.
This life was a
fascinating game to him.
And he wouldn't trade
it for anything!
Especially not to
be a part of you!
You fool, you're mine
whether you like it or not.
So just accept it.
[CELL] Go ahead and try! But how
many seconds will you need?
At least a few to
gather energy for the blast!
But I will stop
you before then!
All I need is a
second to get to you,
but you'll need at least a
handful to get the job done!
[CELL chuckles]
Add it up.
[CELL] Come to me.
[ANDROID 16 groans]
No!
[ANDROID 18 growls]
Huh?
What does that no count
think he's doing?
[TIEN] I'm doing the only right
thing... I'm stopping you.
You fool! You've seen, you
know you're no match for me!
[TIEN] I might be just a pothole
in the road to you, big guy!
But it's going to be
one heck of a deep pothole!
Take this, you!
[TIEN yells]
[TIEN] Tri-Beam! Haaa!
[ANDROID 18 grunts,
CELL yells]
Oh, no!
Tien just jumped in, didn't he?!
We had a plan!
He's not even supposed to
be there! What's the deal?
[ANDROID 16]
18... Are you okay?
[ANDROID 18]
I'm fine, I think.
[TIEN]
There you go, Cell!
A little greeting
from the "No Count"!
[TIEN] Alright, big guy! I know
you're down there somewhere!
And I'll bet you're
raging mad, aren't you?
Oh boy, Tien! You've
really done it this time!
Why are you still here?!
Get out of here right now!
[CELL yells]
[TIEN bellows]
[CELL grunts]
Can you fly?
I will try to.
[CELL yells]
[TIEN yells]
[CELL grunts]
[TIEN yelling]
[CELL grunting]
He's putting out
too much energy!
Darn it!
What's he doing?!
He knows that he can't
sustain an effort like that!
We're gonna lose him!
[TIEN yells]
[CELL shouts]
[ANDROID 16]
You go, 18..
I do not think...
I can fly.. anymore..
[ANDROID 18]
Yes, you can! Let's go!
[TIEN yells]
[yelling continues]
[CELL shouts]
No, Tien!
Get out of there!
[NARRATOR]
Tien's going all out,
but how much longer
can he hold on?
With Cell on the rampage,
is there any hope left
for the valiant warrior?
Can Vegeta and Trunks
complete their training
in the pendulum room
in time to lend a hand?
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!