[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z...
Kaio-Ken! Times two!
[NARRATOR] Goku and Vegeta
went head-to-head
in a contest of
strength and skill,
increasing their levels of
power with every attack.
But as the
battle raged on,
it was clear that Vegeta
still had the upperhand.
Goku soon realized
his only hope
for defeating the evil
Saiyan was to push himself
beyond the limits
of his training,
to a level King Kai had warned
him never to attempt...
And though Vegeta, with his
seemingly unstoppable power,
loomed over him like a
predator toying with its prey,
Goku stood his ground as he
prepared to launch himself
back into the fight!
[GOKU] Time to see
what I'm made of...
[NARRATOR] Can Goku
find the strength
to stop the ruthless Vegeta?
Alright, here goes nothing...
Kaio-Ken Attack times three!
[NARRATOR]
Stay tuned!
Haah!
[thinking]
Hm? What's this all about?
[GOKU growling]
Uh...
[ROSHI]
Bulma?
[CHICHI]
What is it?
Uhh... Ah!
No! I told him not
to go over a double!
His body isn't trained to
handle more than that!
[BUBBLES chattering]
[thinking] Oh, Goku...
Please, be careful!
[GOKU'S shouts echoing]
[shouting]
[shouting continuing]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yelling]
[yelling continues]
[GOKU yelling, skin sizziling]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU bellowing]
[VEGETA grunting]
Haa...
[grunting continues]
[GOKU yelling]
Ah! Ugh!
[yelling continues]
[GOKU] Hrrgh!
Urgh!
[GOKU growling]
[growling continues]
[VEGETA grunting]
[growling, grunting]
Wow! Goku!
[GOKU] Eurgh!
[VEGETA snarling]
[VEGETA yelling]
[VEGETA growling]
Uurgh...
[VEGETA] Waugh!
[grunting]
[growling]
Eugh... Gaah...
Hrrgh!
[YAJIROBE]
He's winning!
All right! Goku might just
beat this guy after all!
[OX KING] Goku must be putting
up one heck of a fight, ChiChi!
If he did this
to the scouter.
There's no telling
how powerful he is...
But what
about Gohan?
I wanna know what's
happened to him!
Baba, can't you
get it to work?
Hmm... I'm trying dear. There's
just so much interference
from their
power levels...
Well, I hope you get
it working soon!
I'm tired of not knowing
what's going on out there!
His power did knock out
the scouter... So, uh...
Maybe he's
already won!
[BULMA] Yeah!
I don't know guys, but
I seriously doubt it.
[ROSHI] The power measured
from Goku was unstable.
Think about it... A candle
flickers most violently
just before
it burns out.
[CHICHI] You're saying
that Goku's in trouble?!
[ROSHI] No, I'm
talkin' about candles...
Of course he's in trouble!
[BABA] Come on,
crystal ball!
Hrgh!
[grunting]
[VEGETA shouting]
[shouting continues]
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA yelling]
[GOKU growling]
[VEGETA grunting]
[gasping]
[thinking] His power...
How could he be so strong?
He's blocking my attacks
like they were nothing!
What a guy! He won't quit!
That's alright, I won't either!
Aaughh!
But... My body might...
[thinking] What are
you waiting for, Goku?
You've got him right
where you want him!
[VEGETA] This shouldn't
be happening!
I don't
understand!
I am a Super Elite!
Now, he's sealed his fate!
This planet
is history!
I'll destroy
everything! Everything!
Do you hear me, Kakarot?
You're finished!
[thinking] Uh-oh!
This isn't good!
I still haven't recovered
from the last attack!
Come on, body...
Don't give out on me now!
[VEGETA panting]
Rrgh!
[VEGETA] Who does this fool
think he's dealing with?!
He's beneath me!
I'll show him...
I'll show them all! I'll
reduce this place to ashes!
Raaugh!
Kakarot!
Dodge this next
attack if you can!
But know that
if you do,
your precious little
planet will be gone!
No! You can't!
[VEGETA] The choice
is yours, Kakarot!
But either way...
you are going to perish!
[VEGETA laughing]
No, not yet!
I'm worn out!
[YAJIROBE whimpering]
[VEGETA yelling]
I-I don't have any time!
It's now or never!
[GOKU] Kaio-Ken times three!
[GOKU yelling]
[GOKU] Let's see how he
likes a Kamehameha!
Ka... Me...
[VEGETA yelling]
Ha...
[VEGETA] Now, Kakarot!
Pepare yourself for oblivion!
Me...
Gallic Gun!
Yaah!
Oh, no! If I knew this
was going to happen,
I would've eaten more
pizza and ice cream!
Haa!
[YAJIROBE grunting]
[GOKU yelling]
It can't be! His beam is
as strong as my Gallic Gun!
[GOKU growling]
[VEGETA growling]
Ohh!
[OOLONG] Hey, look!
[ROSHI] Easy there, sis!
Woah!
Your crystal ball must
be transmitting
some of the energy those
two are releasing...
[ROSHI] I'm not sure
how much more of this
that ball
can handle!
[BABA]
Why, my ball can--
[ALL screaming]
[GOKU grunting]
Raaugh!
[thinking] I've got
to take it further...
Kaio-Ken!
No! Goku!
[GOKU] Times four!
No! Noooo!
[VEGETA screaming]
[GOKU panting]
[YAJIROBE grunting]
My body...
I'm... not... dead?
That... means...
he did it!
Goku, you did it!
Heh, heh, heh, heh!
Alright! Way to go!
[YAJIROBE chuckling]
Huh?
Oh, hey, Yajirobe!
Where did you come from?
Who me? I've been
here the whole time!
You didn't see me
cheering you on
from behind the
rocks back there?
Heh, heh, heh... Uh, no...
Yeah, I didn't
cheer out loud.
I thought it would
distract you.
But man, I saw the whole
thing! You're awesome!
Yaauugh!
[GOKU panting]
Wow, Goku...
You're all worn out!
Yeah, I think I over
did it a little bit...
Well, that doesn't
surprise me.
You should
pace yourself...
I feel so drained!
My body's thrashed!
I can hardly move!
Yeah, good thing
it's over!
Uh, isn't it?
Well, at this
particular moment,
things are
looking pretty good.
I don't think he's
enjoying himself!
Wow! How cool!
Standing together...
The Earth's
greatest defenders.
Not quite...
That didn't stop him...
Just slowed him
down a little...
I think he'll be
coming back soon...
Y-You sure?
Mm-hmm...
[YAJIROBE] See ya, Goku!
Looks like you got it
all under control!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA] Aaagh!
Why?! Why is his power
superior to mine?!
I am the most powerful
Saiyan in the universe!
He should be kneeling before
me, begging for mercy!
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA panting]
Wait a minute... Kakarot
doesn't have a tail,
which means there's no way he
can transform! I've got him!
Heh, ha, ha, ha!
I'll change into the giant ape
and crush him where he stands!
I hate him for
forcing me to do this!
That form is meant to
level civilizations
and destroy planets,
and now I'm using it
to wipe out one stubborn, little
insect... How repugnant!
All I need is the light
from this planet's moon
for this transformation
to take place...
But where is it?
The moon should
be out by now...
[KING KAI thinking] He can
look for it all he wants,
but he won't
find it...
The Earth doesn't
have a moon anymore!
Piccolo destroyed
the moon,
fearing and anticipating
this very situation.
But it
doesn't matter,
because Goku has used
up all of his energy.
Ape or no ape, he's in
no shape to face anyone!
If he can't regain
his strength in time,
his only option will be
to use the Spirit Bomb!
If he can manage to
pull one together
and blast it at Vegeta,
he might just make it
out of this alive...
[GOKU thinking] I know
he's up there somewhere...
But what's he doing?
I'm sure he's regained
enough strength by now...
Why hasn't he come
back to attack me?
He's up to something...
I've got to be careful.
[VEGETA] Oh, come on!
What have they done with it?
It's a moon... It's not like
you can hide it anywhere!
It can only mean
one thing...
Someone on this stinking
planet had enough foresight
to know that I
would need it,
and they've destroyed it to
prevent my transformation...
No matter...
We Saiyans have encountered
this problem before,
and devised a way
to deal with it...
They haven't
stopped me,
they've only delayed
the inevitable!
[VEGETA laughing]
Come on!
I'm ready...
[thinking] I've only
got one shot...
The Spirit Bomb!
I just hope I still have
the strength to do it...
[VEGETA] So, Kakarot...
You think you
can outsmart me?
Destroying the moon
won't stop anything!
Moon? What
about the moon?
Don't play innocent
with me, Kakarot!
Just know that your
efforts were in vain
because I don't need the moon
to complete my transformation!
Transformation?
[VEGETA] The moon merely
reflects the rays of the sun!
But as they're
being reflected...
A new energy called
Blutz Wave is created
and added to
their composition.
These waves cause
the transformation,
not the moonlight by itself,
as you may have believed...
What is he
talking about?
[VEGETA] Although moonlight
is a natural source of
Blutz Wave power, it is not the
only way to form this energy...
There is another way...
[VEGETA] We Saiyans realized
that we were at the mercy
of the moonlight on
whatever planet we were on,
unable to control the
length of day or night.
It was completely
unpredictable,
and held our power
at a disadvantage...
Until we
discovered a way
to artificially create
our own moonlight!
[VEGETA laughing]
[VEGETA] By channeling the
energy from within ourselves
and combining it with the
planet's atmosphere...
We can make a synthetic moon,
complete with Blutz Waves,
anytime and anywhere
we want to!
As soon as I release
this into the sky,
the transformation
will begin,
and there's nothing
you can do about it!
[VEGETA laughing]
Uuraagh!
Oh, no!
Ahh... Aaah!
[VEGETA] Bear witness
to the ultimate power
of the Saiyans,
Kakarot.
The Giant Ape!
Destroyer of Planets!
Soon, this world will
feel my wrath...
Now, let it begin!
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA panting]
[GOKU gasps]
What? No way! I've got a
bad feeling about this...
If I don't think
of something soon,
I'll have a much bigger
problem on my hands...
No! Goku! You can't
let him change!
[VEGETA] Yes! Yes!
I can feel it!
The power, coursing through my
veins, burning inside me!
[VEGETA laughing]
[laughing continues]
[KING KAI whimpering]
Now, it's too late...
[VEGETA snarling]
Eh?
Something's not right...
[APE VEGETA roaring]
[roaring continues]
[roaring]
[GOKU sputtering]
[APE VEGETA roaring]
[NARRATOR] Consumed
with rage and fury,
Vegeta has summoned forth the
ultimate power from within,
and plans to use it to
destroy not only Goku,
but the entire planet!
Will he succeed in
his apocalyptic plans?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!