Last time, on
Dragon Ball Z!
Meanwhile, Yamcha,
Chiaotzu, and Tien
But Piccolo had no patience
for such foolish games.
Hang on tight, kid!
Now, Krillin and Dende race
to find the Eldest Namek,
Your fighting skills
have come a long way
Will Vegeta's overconfidence
be his undoing?
So I'm not strong enough
to beat you? Funny.
That's right... You figured
it out... I knew you would.
You crack me up!
Go ahead.
Laugh if you want.
It's time I showed
you my true power.
You ever hear the saying,
beauty is only skin deep?
Is that so? Well, you'll
pardon me if I hadn't noticed.
Now you're being much
too hasty, Vegeta...
Let's see it!
All right, then... So be it.
but consider yourself warned.
What the-
As I said, you only saw the
'beauty' side of me before.
Hey, Dende.
It's not far now...
Good. We gotta hurry.
Y'know, there's something I've
been meaning to ask you...
But it's still so bright. I
mean, doesn't your sun set?
Not all at once.
We have three
different suns.
So, you're saying that on your
planet, you never have night?
No, we don't.
No wonder you're green...
Guess this means it's
time to take a break...
All right, I've almost
got the hang of this
If I can keep going
at this rate,
I wonder how Yamcha,
Tien, and Piccolo
I hope it's
going okay...
Goku... Listen to me!
All you'd do
is provoke him!
But what about
the Dragon Balls?
No! You have
to promise me!
Come on...
Absolutely
nooooot!
That's it! I have
to train harder!
Come here!
Oh no you don't!
Monkey!
Get 'im!
Huh, well whadda'
you know!
No! I won't lose!
And you wouldn't believe me
when I said you couldn't win!
Oh, man... Even from
this far away...
Enough of this, I'm
through toying with you.
No... I won't be defeated
like this... I can't!
It's 'lights out'
for you, Vegeta!
There...
Sweet dreams, prince.
Ah, how perfect...
Oh well.. It serves him
right for making me go
Oh, how did I ever
get into this mess?
How can you be so calm
at a time like this?
It's easy, Bulma...
Well, I really hope
he gets here soon...
I just hope Krillin and
Dende are still doing okay...
The power
levels dropped...
So then, who do
you think won?
I don't know...
Which way? Should I just keep
flying straight, or what?
Actually, I think it's
a little bit to the left.
Look, there! It's just up
ahead, on top of that bluff!
Yeah, I see it...
Looks like
we made it...
Come on, Krillin. We'll find
the Eldest Namek inside.
Are you sure?
It's so quiet. Maybe
they got him already...
oh no...
Hey, Nail! Am I ever glad
to see you're all right!
This guy looks
just like Piccolo!
It's good to see
you again, Dende...
So, then Guru knows
about everything
Well, that's some
good news, at least...
There is much to
discuss. Come with me.
Wait, Nail... If Guru already
knows what's happening...
Guru is very old. He knows
his time is drawing near.
There is little more
I can do for him
Oh no... I knew
he was old...
Please.
Come, Dende.
This guy's
different
Up.
Master, I've brought Dende
and his Earth friend.
Whoa... He's huge!
Welcome, friend...
It is my great honor
Oh, well, uh, there's no
need to thank me. Really!
Zarbon, you've made
your last mistake...
Vegeta has survived!