[NARRATOR] Previously on
Dragon Ball Z,
Videl continued her desperate
bid to beat Spopovitch,
but the super-charged psycho
was able to counter
her every move with
his own punishing attacks!
Gohan watched in horror as
Videl was batted about the ring
like a rag doll.
And it didn't take long for
Spopovitch's brutal attack
to push the young hero
over the edge...
[GOHAN] This has gone on
way too long!
I'm taking him down!
[NARRATOR]
But before Gohan could act,
Spopovitch's fun was cut short
by his mysterious partner, Yamu.
[YAMU] Don't you remember that
we have
far more important things to do?
Finish it immediately!
Uh? Oh my... Videl? It's over!
She's out of the ring!
[NARRATOR] Videl fought
bravely until the end,
but Spopovitch's seemingly
endless supply
of supernatural strength
had guaranteed him
the victory from the start.
And though the fight may be
over, for Videl,
the real battle has just begun
today on Dragon Ball Z!
Uhh...?
[GOHAN thinking] I wonder
what's taking Dad so long?
Mr. Satan wants us to make sure
no one disturbs his daughter.
[GOHAN] Krillin,
I'm gonna go see Videl.
Sure...
But what about your dad?
Don't you want to wait for him?
He went to Korin's to get
some Senzu beans, remember?
Yeah! But how can I just
stand around like this
when I know Videl's
in the hospital?!
There's got to be
some way I can help...
Good luck.
[GOHAN] Hmm?
[KRILLIN chuckles]
You know what?
It sounds to me like
you and Videl
are becoming more
than just friends, huh?
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[VIDEL groans weakly]
Ah! Ah?! Hey, Doc! Are you
sure she'll be alright?!
She'll be fine!
Rest and relaxation
is all she needs now.
[MR. SATAN ] You better be,
'cause if anything happens
to her, I'm gonna
hold you responsible!
[NANCY] Mr. Satan!
Please, open up!
We'd like to know the
condition of your daughter!
Would you care to make a
statement for your fans, sir?
Please! The public
has a right to know!
[SOUND GUY] Uh...
Are you sure he's in there?
[ALL yell]
[SOUND GUY] ...Dude... ahh...
[MR. SATAN growls]
[SOUND GUY] Uh...
[ALL] Huh?
Like, so what's up with,
you know, Videl?
My daughter is just fine...
She's resting comfortably now...
Unfortunately, she is out of
the competition for good.
But you can tell my fans
to expect a big show
at my next match!
Of course.
But is there anything you'd
like to say to Spopovitch?
[MR. SATAN growls]
You better believe there is!
You give him this message:
You tell him that he'd better
watch his back
because Mr. Satan
is coming to get him!
[door slams]
[NANCY] Mr. Satan, wait!
Please,  just one more question!
I gotta get in there...
But there's too many reporters
around the room...
[VIDEL yells]
[grunting, groaning]
[VIDEL] No! I won't give up!
How could Spopovitch
have done this?
That guy's a cream puff!
At least he was...
[CROWD cheering]
[MR. SATAN] Yeaah! All right!
Mr. Satan, the champion
of the world! Yeah!
Oh yeah!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
Spopovitch...
I can't believe they let an
amateur like you
step into the ring...
These are my fans.
Try to give 'em
a good show, okay?
And, hey, look on
the bright side:
At least you're gonna get
beat by a real champ!
Oh yeah?! I'll show you!
[grunting]
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[SPOPOVITCH gasps]
So... You had enough?
[SPOPOVITCH] No way!
[MR. SATAN grunts]
[ANNOUNCER]
Spopovitch is out of the ring!
Mr. Satan has won the match!
Videl... How could you lose?
He's a wimp!
You should have won!
I taught you everything
I know about martial arts!
How could you possibly
need more than that?!
Hey, maybe you were
distracted by that skinny kid
who brought you
to the hospital...
Well, he won't
bother you anymore!
[VIDEL] Gohan...
[MR. SATAN snarls]
[SHARPNER] The coast
is clear. C'mon!
Do you think Videl
will be okay?
[SHARPNER thinking] That was
Saiyaman I saw with Videl.
I've got to find out
who he is...
If only my camera hadn't broken,
I'd have a picture
of him right now!
[laughter,
GOHAN gasps]
[shutter clicks]
Perfect!
I couldn't see it with the
shutter moving,
but it's gotta be on film!
And as soon as
I develop these pics,
I can make him
into a laughing stock
and Videl will just
have to like me!
[SHARPNER yelps]
[SHARPNER thinking]
He got lucky,
but sooner or later
he's gonna slip up!
[ERASA] Sharpner! Sharpner!
Do you think she'll
be all right?
Don't worry! I'll
find out who he is!
You can count on it!
[ERASA] Hmm?
[SHARPNER gasps]
Look! It's Saiyaman!
[GOHAN] Huh?!
Know what?
He really does look
kinda familiar to me.
I gotta find out
who that guy is!
[GOHAN] Hey, Krillin,
shouldn't Dad be back?
[KRILLIN] Mm-hmm. I don't know
what's taking him so long.
I don't want
to rush you, Goku,
but aren't you
forgetting something?
Don't they need you
back on Earth?
Yeah, I know.
But it's just that they don't
have good food like this
at Grand Kai's place.
This is delicious!
Yes...
But you came here for Senzu
beans not to stuff your face.
[GOKU] Yeah you're right,
as usual!
Thanks for the chow.
I tell you, Korin, there's
something really strange
about those guys
Spopovitch and Yamu...
We'd better keep
our eyes on them.
Spopovitch. The one we're
after may be one of them.
Don't worry...
We'll know soon
enough with this...
We'll wait 'til the next match.
[SPOPOVITCH] Mm-hmm.
You know what to do, Kibito.
My Gohan will be
fighting next!
Yeah, he's fighting
that Kibito guy.
Well, "Kibito, Shamito!"
My Gohan can take him
no problem!
Well I should hope so...
It'll be kind of hard
to win the tournament
if Gohan gets beat
in the first round
--[ROSHI chuckles]
--My boy will come through
for me. We really
need that prize money!
Yeah! Get him, Gohan!
ChiChi, be quiet!
Gohan's identity is
supposed to be a secret!
[CHICHI gasps]
[CHICHI] Oh, that's right!
I forgot about that!
Ladies and gentlemen, are you
ready for the fourth match?!
[CROWD cheers]
[FRIAR A] Hey, Mr. Announcer!
[whispering]
Hey! Everyone,
please listen to this!
I have some very
good news about Videl:
She's fine.
And once she gets some rest,
the doctor says she's expected
to make a full recovery.
How about that?!
[CROWD cheers]
And here we go!
Fighters to the ring, please.
In this match, Kibito
will battle against the--
Uh... Excuse me, sir!
Could I have a little
more time please?
Y'see, my dad's gone
to get some medicine
that will make
Videl feel better,
but I'm afraid
he's not back yet.
I want to make sure she gets
it before I start the match!
It's for Videl? Then take
all the time that you need.
Thanks a lot.
Sit tight, folks, the next
match has been delayed!
[CROWD jeers]
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN] Come on, Dad!
Where are you?
Videl needs those
Senzu beans now!
[FRIAR A] You really should
get this match underway...
The crowd is getting restless
and I hate to think
what they'll do if
they have to wait any longer.
[FRIAR B] Yeah...
What's the hold up?!
[VEGETA gasps]
--Hey!
--Hey, Dad!
Did you get the Senzu beans?
Yep. Korin and Yajirobe
only had three left,
but they're all yours
if you want them!
[GOHAN] You bet I do!
Sure... Better get
these to Videl.
[GOKU] Here ya go.
[GOHAN] All right!
[GOHAN laughs]
Thanks a lot!
[GOHAN] Hey, hold on, big guy!
I'll be right back!
I promise!
[GOKU thinking]
This Kibito guy looks like
a pretty serious fighter. And
for that matter, so does Shin!
Anyone who can scare
Piccolo the way he did
must be pretty awesome!
[VEGETA thinking]
Hmph. Look at Kakarot...
Checking out his competition?
He's wasting his time...
I'm the one he should be
worrying about.
[GOTEN grunts]
[TRUNKS] Hey, Goten!
What did your dad give to Gohan?
[GOTEN] I don't know...
I bet it was something that's
going to give Gohan
some kind of super strength so
he can win his next match
against that Kibito.
[GOTEN] Nah! Gohan's
tough enough on his own.
[TRUNKS] Well I hope
they get started soon!
We're in the seventh match
and when we get out there
somebody is gonna
get their butt kicked!
[GOTEN grunts]
Hey, Trunks, how come I
have to be on the bottom?
[NANCY] How long will Videl
be in the hospital?
Is she okay?!
[VIDEL groans]
Videl?
Hi, Dad...
Oh, good. You're awake.
[NANCY] I'm telling you, this is
going to be the--
[GOHAN] Excuse me,
coming through!
Come on! Open up!
[DOCTOR yells]
[GOHAN] Videl! I've
got something for ya!
[MR. SATAN] Hey, who said
you could come in here?!
Now get out!
Videl needs her rest!
Sorry for the intrusion.
[MR. SATAN]
You got some nerve, kid.
[MR. SATAN growls]
Hi... Gohan... Hey... What's up?
Quiet... Here, take this.
It'll make you feel better.
It's a Senzu bean!
Hold it! Don't give my patient
anything funny now, young man.
Yeah, and don't think you can
impress my daughter with a bean!
[GOHAN] Trust me, sir, this will
make her as good as new!
[MR. SATAN] No way! No bean!
[VIDEL] Please, Daddy...
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[yelling]
I trust you, Gohan...
And I...
Videl, no! This weird kid
doesn't know what he's doing!
Come on, Doc! Say something!
Yes... S-Stop that!
Videl!
No! Spit it out! Spit it out!
I have a match to go to now.
[NANCY] This is going to be a
big story, I'm telling you--
--[REPORTERS gasping]
--[MR. SATAN] Hey!
Come back here!
Yeah! You better run!
And you better stay away
from my daughter!
Videl, no!
[MR. SATAN squeals]
I'm all better now!
[VIDEL laughs]
[BOTH squeal]
[GOHAN] Thanks for waiting!
Now I'm ready!
[KIBITO grunts]
Ladies and gentlemen,
so sorry to keep you waiting.
Now let's get started!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Here we
go with the fourth match
of this competition!
Kibito versus the
Great Saiyaman!
I still think he looks
like someone...
Oh, yeah! He looks
like Gohan, yeah.
Come on,
let me take a look!
Yeah! He's got the same haircut.
I was noticing it
through the binoculars,
but I can't anymore
'cause you took 'em.
I would like them back...
It is Gohan! How could
I have missed it?!
It's been him all along!
Gohan? No way!
If that is him I bet
he just signed up secretly
and borrowed the name!
Erasa, why would he do
something like that?
Well, because he's shy!
That's why!
If he's not Saiyaman,
he's about to be in big trouble!
Nothing fixes trouble like
cheering! Let's all yell!
[ERASA &amp; SHARPNER &amp; CLASSMATE]
You can do it, Gohan!
We got Gohan, so there!
You're great, Gohan!
Yeah! Go Gohan! Yeah!
You can do it, Gohan!
Hit him, you're strong!
[GOHAN groans]
It's him. I know it's him.
But how can they
tell that it's me?!
[thinking] I guess my
disguise is no good
without the covering
on my head...
Oh well, won't be needing
these shades anymore.
[GOHAN chuckles sheepishly]
[CLASSMATE] Thatta boy, Gohan!
[ERASA] Yeah!
Now we can see your face!
[GOHAN] Yeah, I know... Thanks!
Just like that...
And after all the effort I put
into finding out who he was...
YOU BROKE MY CAMERA!
[ANNOUNCER] Uh... I'm sure
our two fierce competitors
are ready to lock
horns at any moment!
Uh... Come on, guys,
we're all waiting!
[KIBITO grunts]
[GOHAN thinking]
What do I do now?
Bulma's idea to wear a
disguise worked great,
but without it,
I'm totally exposed!
If I show my powers now, I won't
be able to go back to school...
They'll think I'm a freak!
And this guy doesn't exactly
look like a pushover either.
Gohan, I am curious to see
your Super Saiyan powers.
Show them to me!
We may be able to use them!
Huh? Hey?! Hold on!
How do you know
I'm a Super Saiyan?!
And what do you mean by
"we may be able to use them"?
[KIBITO]
You'll know more in time.
Show me your
Super Saiyan powers now!
Now it begins...
Uh? Is this
some kind of a joke?
I'm not going to
transform out here
in front of all these people!
[KRILLIN] They're not fighting.
What are they doing?
They're just talking.
[GOKU] Kibito wants to see him
become a Super Saiyan!
[KRILLIN] Hm?
[YAMU] Spopovitch,
what does it say?
No... It's not them...
Low energy.
[PICCOLO] Gohan!
'Kay, here goes.
What is it, Piccolo?
What's happening out there?
I'm not sure, Goku...
We'll see...
[SUPREME KAI] It's time...
You do not need
to worry about Gohan.
He will be fine.
But no matter what happens,
I want you to promise me
you'll stay out of the ring.
Do you understand?
What? No way!
What do you want with Gohan?
[PICCOLO]
He wants to see his power...
Well? Let's see it.
[GOHAN] Ah, this is gonna
get me kicked out of school!
All right, then...
You asked for it!
I don't know you and you're
telling me what to do?
Who do you think you are?
Vegeta, show him
some respect...
That is no way to be
talking to the Supreme Kai!
[gasping]
I heard stories
from King Kai,
but I thought they
were just stories!
Shin! You're the Supreme Kai?!
--[MAN A] Hey, you losers!
--[CROWD jeering, yelling]
[MAN B] Come on,
start fighting, you sissies!
[MAN C] What is this?! Is this a
staring contest or something?!
[MAN D] I want my money back!
Oh no... Uh...
Everyone, please remain calm!
[ANNOUNCER grunts]
[CHICHI growls]
Keep your shirts on!
You want a show?!
You're gonna get a show!
My son Gohan always delivers!
[NARRATOR]
All eyes are on Gohan...
A suspicious group of spectators
watch his every move
from the sidelines.
Shin, the Supreme Kai,
wants no one to interfere
with Gohan's transformation.
Meanwhile, Spopovitch and Yamu
closely monitor
the fighters' power levels.
But for what purpose?
[NARRATOR] What dark designs
lurk beneath the surface
of the World Martial
Arts Tournament?
Shin, Kibito, Spopovitch, Yamu--
Which of these mysterious
fighters are friends?
And which are foes?
As Gohan begins his
powerful transformation,
the answers to these and other
important questions
are sure to come to light!