[birds chirping]
Gosh Dad, what's the deal?
Man, don't you think
it's been long enough?
Where in the world are you?
[TORTOISE] Oh boy,
here he goes again!
[KRILLIN grunting]
Ka.. me.. ha.. me...
Ha!
[explosion]
Oooh, yea!
[TORTOISE]
Look out below!
Ah! Tidal wave!
Yikes!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Still not good enough!
[ROSHI snoring]
Hmm?
[ROSHI] He's been so serious
since he broke up with Maron!
No way! That won't cut it! Yeah!
I gotta turn it up a notch!
[ROSHI humming]
You know I bet
I could teach Krillin
a thing or two about
getting along with the ladies!
Getting them mad,
you mean!
[ROSHI yells]
[KRILLIN thinking] I know
you'll be back someday, Goku!
And whatever it is
that you're called to do,
I'll be here to help!
I'll be ready!
[GOHAN humming]
[CHICHI]
Gohan? Gohan?
[knocking on door]
Hey, you! There you are! Good!
Huh? What's up?
Ahhh!
[crash]
Gohan! You're being silly!
[GOHAN laughing]
Gohan! We have
a house guest! Say hi!
This is Mister Shu! He is
going to be your new tutor!
But Mom, why?
Mr. Shu is going to help you
take your studies to
the next level, Gohan!
And I was thinking that you
might want to get started today!
Can't I just study harder and
forget about the tutor? Please?
No! N-O No! And that's
the final word, Gohan!
Goodness! Why me?
First my husband leaves, then my
son starts rebelling against me!
Why me? Why?
Oh, it just isn't fair!
I feel so vulnerable!
Where did I go wrong?!
Ahem...
Gohan! It's time you
two got started!
There you go Mr. Shu,
he's all yours now!
Very well! I'll do what I can!
Madame, I'm very strict!
Oftentimes, slow
children like this
just need a little discipline!
My Gohan is not slow,
Mister Shu!
Of course not! Every parent
thinks their child is a prodigy!
I'm sure he's brilliant,
that's why you hired a tutor...
Now, please excuse us!
We have work to do!
Cat loves food!
Yea, yea, yea, yeah!
You goof! You're such a nut!
Where did you come up with that?
That was from an old
cat food commercial!
Puar hates it when I do that!
I ate catfood once! Oh man!
I thought it was tuna fish!
I had a weird dream last
night that Vegeta came back!
What?! Vegeta?!
You dreamt about him?!
You know, actually he was
pretty nice to me in the dream,
and a good
kisser to boot!
What? You kissed him?
It was just a dream, Yamcha!
You poor sap! You're jealous,
aren't you?! Admit it!
Right!
Speaking of Vegeta your Dad said
he should be running out of fuel
soon!
Hm?! Vegeta's running out of
fuel!
Man! Aw...
Please do not talk slang
when you're in my presence!
And I can see two
mistakes on here already!
Mistakes are to learn from!
And smarting off
to your instructor
is a mistake I'll teach you
not to make again!
Yes, that might be the toughest
lesson you've ever learned!
It hurt me to do it, but I'm
sure your mother will appreciate
the end result!
Gosh, this is so exciting!
Gohan's finally going to
get the attention he deserves!
Ivy-league, here we come!
How dare you, you insolent brat!
This is what you get when
you back talk to Mister Shu!
[whipping continues]
[MR. SHU] I've dealt
with your kind before!
Oh, yes! Little rebel punks!
Abandoned by their fathers!
But they all come
around, eventually!
[birds chirping]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN]
Oh, man.
[GOHAN yawns]
Hey! What's up?!
Oh! Shhh!
Let's go, quick! Man,
you're a life saver, Icarus!
Hey! Wait for me!
[GOHAN giggling]
Icarus, where are you?!
[GOHAN whimpering]
Hm? Hey! Hi, Gohan!
Dad, is it really you?!
[GOKU chuckles]
Of course it is!
Now don't I get
a hug, tough guy?
Dad!
Daddy, it's really you!
Daddy!
Daddy, it's you! I can't
believe it! It's you! It's you!
It's okay, Gohan!
It's okay!
Huh?! Oh my goodness!
Hey, hon! Sorry, I'm late!
I guess I shouldn't have
taken that left turn at Mars!
No problem!
What's a year and a half?!
Something smells good!
Wow! I hope that's our dinner!
Huh? It is!
But you're not
going to get any
if you go through the window,
Goku. You know better!
C'mon! Give me a break!
I just got home!
[CHICHI growls]
He's back!
I can't believe it!
[GOHAN] So what happened
up there on Namek, Dad?
What happened to Frieza?
[GOKU] Well, it's
a long story, Gohan!
And I doubt Mom wants to
hear it right before dinner!
Ok!
So where have
you been all this time, Dad?
Aw, come on, Daddy! You can
tell me that much, can't you?!
[GOKU growls]
Your Dad isn't coming back!
He's a loser!
He's nothing but a loser!
No no no!
[MR. SHU] Ahhh!
Let go! Please kid!
Let go!
You're killing me! Ah-ah!
I beg of you!
Please let go of me!
My gosh! What are you?!
You... you mad man!
You almost broke my arm!
How dare you attack
me like that!
I was dreaming!
Well it's about time
you came to your senses!
That's your father's
influence, I'll bet!
Martial Arts...
I've heard the talk, yes.
He's a brainless brute!
[GOHAN growls]
How dare you! You punk!
Are you challenging me?!
Well, take this!
Unhand me you barbarian!
For your information, Mister
Shu, my father is not a brute!
He's a great man!
Is that clear?!
You wouldn't!
Defend my Dad's honor?
You better believe I will!
Let's talk about this! With
your Mother here of course!
Hello! Miss ChiChi!
Alright! Put 'em up!
Gohan? What are you doing?!
Me? Nothin'
[MR. SHU] Yes, although he can
appear to be quite normal...
You're son is afflicted with
what I call the demon-seed!
[GOHAN growls]
Yes, it is a seed of rebellion
and contempt for his superiors!
You can let this seed grow,
or nip it in the bud!
Gohan!
Ah, yes! He's driven
to fight like his Father!
What? That's not true!
Oh! My foot it's not!
My Dad's a saint
compared to you!
What? How dare you!
[GOHAN growls]
Ah, that's better! A little
discipline works miracles!
You just need a father!
Look! Mister!
I have a Father!
You do! Where is he! Oh he's
gone off fighting somewhere!
Right! Right!
Am I right!
Of course I'm right!
It's only natural
that the child
should want to follow in
his father's violent footsteps
After being abandoned
by the worthless father,
he fights to measure up!
A vicious cycle!
Like father, like son!
[MR. SHU laughs]
[CHICHI growls]
Get out of our house!
[MR. SHU yells]
Wow! Nice throw!
Thank you.
You'll pay for this! Nobody
throws Mister Shu! How dare you!
[CHICHI]
Get out of here!
And don't come back!
Oh! I didn't know we had
any guests dropping by!
Goodness! I definitely need
to put on another pot of tea!
Vegeta! What do you want?
Oh my! Maybe you'd
prefer some coffee?
I was hoping that Kakarot
might have finally returned?
Hm? What? No way! You
never found him in space?
Don't remind me!
I'm angry enough
to hurt somebody!
And, pounding you might
just be the therapy I need!
Hey, guys!
What's that awful smell!
Oh, it's you!
When's the last time
you bathed there, bud?
You need a bath!
Please! This way!
Well? What? Do you want me
to roll out the red carpet?
[VEGETA growls]
[YAMCHA]
Unreal!
I hope she knows
what she's doing!
Hey! Does anyone take lemon?
[VEGETA muttering]
Hey, you! I left you
some fresh clothes!
[BULMA] Hello?!
You alive in there?!
I heard you!
You can leave now!
Why yes, master!
Your wish is my command!
The female species!
Such an enigma!
Yeah that Vegeta is
nothing but trouble!
He's so unpredictable, it's hard
to tell what his motives are!
I think he just
wants to find Goku!
Poor guy!
He's obsessed!
He's used to getting
what he wants!
That's all! He's like
a spoiled little kid!
Man, sounds like you!
[VEGETA] Hello! Servant woman!
Bring me a drying cloth at once!
[BULMA growls]
[VEGETA] Woman!
Can you hear me?
I hear you!
But my name is Bulma!
And I am not your servant!
So say please!
[VEGETA] Forget about
the stupid drying cloth then!
Suit yourself!
Drip dry, you jerk!
[VEGETA] What in the--?! Is
this some kind of joke?!
Is what a joke?
These garments that you left!
Are they for
a man or a woman?
They're pink!
[BULMA] C'mon!
It's the style here!
Men in pink!
How bizarre!
[EVERYONE laughing]
[VEGETA] This is ridiculous!
I'm a warrior!
Not a variety of flower!
Well you smell good!
[EVERYONE laughing]
Stop that! Stop it
or I'll blast you all!
Loosen up!
Fighting's no fun! Just relax!
[VEGETA growls]
If you want to find Goku,
just stay here! He'll come!
I've known Goku since
he was five years old!
Trust me! He'll be back!
I just know he will!
[OX-KING laughing]
ChiChi, darling, you threw
him right out of the window?
Poor guy! Oh, man! Should've
known! Like husband, like wife!
[OX-KING laughing]
Sshh! Gohan's studying, Daddy!
Oops! Sorry.
And then you chased him off
the property! Oh, dear!
[OX-KING laughing]
[CHICHI] Daddy, please!
Control yourself!
It can't be!
[phone ringing]
ring, ring, ring
Do you feel that?!
Holy cow!
[GOHAN] I know! I feel
it too! This isn't good!
But who is it? It can't
be you know who, could it?!
[KRILLIN] I'm afraid so!
We have to be strong, Gohan!
Right.
[KRILLIN] Man! I knew it
was too good to be true!
Suit up, we've got
some planning to do, bro...
Right! Will do!
Dad, where are you?
[BUBBLES in distress]
Oooh, eeee, oooo, ahh, ahh...!
Yes, yes, I know, Bubbles,
yes! I can feel it too!
There's two of them, Chiaotzu!
My gosh! I've never
felt anything like it!
Tien, I'm scared!
Oh, man, Bulma!
This is great!
I'm piggin' out here!
So he failed after all! Frieza's
still alive, and he's coming!
Wait! How do you know?! Maybe it
could be somebody else! Come on!
I know! I make it my
business to know! Unlike you!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Hey, Vegeta!
Would you like a little
more barbecue sauce
on your spare ribs?!
Sure, why not.
Well, my money's on you guys!
We can leave if you
want to fight 'em here!
[PICCOLO growling]
Frieza, there's no way!
[FRIEZA] There it is,
Planet Earth dead ahead!
It's only fitting
that the Saiyan
should call such
a puny planet home!
[KING COLD] Let's finish
this now, son.
We can destroy
the planet from here!
[FRIEZA] Father, that
would spoil all of my fun!
I plan to savor my revenge.
Every... little... bit...
Well, well, look!
A ship on radar!
It seems your Saiyan
friend is almost home!
[FRIEZA laughs]
And when he gets there,
he will find everything he has
ever known or loved in ruins!
Yes...
He will know the
wrath of Frieza!
Oh, man! What a week! First it's
the terror tutor, and now this!
C'mon you!
Oh, no, Dad!
There he goes again!
I need to learn how to fly!
Just look at him!
How can I discipline a kid
who can take-off like that?!
[NARRATOR]
Unfortunately this time Gohan,
it's a game of life or death.
Frieza has survived!
And it looks like double trouble
because his father
King Cold is with him!
On the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!