[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Here, now you have what you
came for. Take it and leave!
[NARRATOR] Having successfully
acquired the fifth Dragon Ball,
Frieza ordered Dodoria to
eliminate the remaining Nameks.
[NARRATOR] It was a task
the ruthless henchman
was only too happy
to carry out.
[DODORIA]
Play dead!
[GOHAN]
Aaahh! Stop it!
[NARRATOR] Not willing
to sit idly by,
Gohan and Krillin
charged to the rescue...
but our heroes soon
found themselves
in a race
for their lives!
Fortunately for them,
the chase was cut short,
as Dodoria had some deep
troubles of his own!
Having watched and waited for
the perfect moment to strike,
Vegeta made his move!
And the Saiyan prince
gave Dodoria a lesson
in ruthlessness he
would not forget.
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] It's the true
might of a Saiyan warrior!
[DODORIA screams]
[DODORIA]
Lord Frieza!
[VEGETA yells]
[DODORIA screaming]
[NARRATOR] In yet another
stunning display of strength,
Vegeta's power has soared
to even greater heights!
It seems none
can oppose him.
Meanwhile, even Goku,
with all of his might,
stands little chance
against this villain.
But in less
than six days,
he will have no
choice but to face him.
Untold dangers await...
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
[VEGETA chuckles]
So long, Dodoria.
After all
his boasting,
in the end he was nothing
more than a sniveling coward.
[chuckles]
But still, I didn't think I
would defeat him so easily.
My powers have grown to exceed
even my own expectations.
Too bad Kakarot
and his friends
can't be here to see
them. Or can they?
I get it...
Those two little brats I chased
out here were Earthlings!
[VEGETA] Hmm, I do sense
a faint power level.
No, two of them.
Flying away.
But it couldn't be anyone
from Earth, could it?
I'd better go
and check it out.
Because if I'm wrong,
and they are here,
I'd hate to miss a chance
to settle the score!
Hey, Krillin!
I recognize this place!
I think we're getting
close to the cave!
Good. 'Cause I was
starting to think
we were getting
lost out here.
Great! Someone's comin'!
We gotta hide, guys. Fast!
Down there
and hurry!
Got it!
I don't know.
It doesn't seem like we've
got a lot of cover here.
Well, it's better than
being up in the air.
Just keep your power low,
and hope we're lucky!
You're worried it's that
monster again, aren'tcha?
Me too.
But I don't think
he'll be able to find
us here, you guys.
Hmm... It's like both of
those powers just disappeared.
But they were just here,
I'm sure of it!
[GOHAN screams]
Oh no, Krillin.
Look! Up there!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[thinking] Oh, great!
This is just what we need!
It's Vegeta! I don't know
how, but he's found us!
[VEGETA] Hmm...?
[ALL whimpering]
[thinking] But I don't get it!
Why would he be looking for us?
And how could he even know
that we're on this planet?!
[whimpering continues]
[GOHAN] It looks
like he's leaving.
Yeah, good. And he wasn't
wearing his scouter.
He must be searching
for something else.
I'm guessing he doesn't
know that we're here, Gohan.
Unless Vegeta's learned
how to sense power levels!
If he has,
we're screwed!
Even if we push our
power down to zero,
he could still
sense him!
[VEGETA] Bah. There's no one
here. Maybe there never was.
Perhaps it was a mistake
to destroy the scouter
before I'd fully
tested my ability!
Hm... But then
again, maybe not.
It's very faint.
But there's
definitely something
coming from
down there!
[GOHAN]
He's coming this way!
[GOHAN screams]
[ALL whimpering]
It's behind
that rock.
Gohan. It's no
good. He's got us.
We can at least lead
him away from the kid.
Let's go!
Huh?!
Now, Gohan!
[VEGETA] Ah!
[KRILLIN &amp; GOHAN scream]
[WHALE moaning]
Damn!
Just a fish.
Oh, forget it. I've wasted
enough time chasing shadows.
There are still two more
Dragon Balls out there,
waiting to be found.
If I can just get to one
before Frieza and hide it,
it'll be enough to stop him
from completing his collection.
Then, it's simply a
matter of biding my time,
waiting for the perfect
opportunity to strike.
It shouldn't take long.
Without their scouters,
I could be breathing
right down their necks
and they wouldn't
even know it!
[VEGETA laughing]
[GOHAN sighs]
Too close!
Oh, man. I just knew
we were goners.
I mean if that whale hadn't
shown up when it did...
Well, I don't even
wanna think about it.
Anyway, I don't
know about you,
but I for one don't
plan to wait around
to see if he comes back.
Let's keep moving.
[GOHAN] Right.
[KRILLIN] That cave is
sounding cozier by the minute.
I am beat!
[GOHAN giggles]
[GOHAN laughs]
[KRILLIN]
Hey, Gohan.
Y'know, I'm sorry
I got you into this.
Maybe it wasn't such a
good idea to come here.
I mean, I wanna wish all
our friends back to life,
but If we try to
compete with Vegeta,
we're just gonna
get ourselves killed.
So, you think we
should give up?
[GOHAN] Hey! Look! There's
the cave! We're safe!
[KRILLIN] Yeah.
Good eye, buddy.
[GOHAN] Bulma!
Bulma?
[GOHAN] I don't
see her anywhere.
Maybe she's way in
the back or something.
I'll go
check it out.
Bulma!
Hey!
Bulma! Come out, come out
wherever you are! Hello!
[GOHAN] A Capsule house?
Well, it's about time
you two came back!
What took you
so long, anyway?
I thought I was
gonna die of boredom!
[GOHAN and KRILLIN
chuckling sheepishly]
Must've been rough...
Hmm?
Hey, what's the deal
with the miniature Piccolo?
He's Namekian, right?
You sure it's a good
idea to bring him here?
Sure. We saved him.
What happened
out there?
How 'bout we
go inside first?
Then we'll tell
you the whole story.
Ah! Oh yeah!
I have a lot to
tell you, too!
I just talked to my
dad a while ago--
Oh, and guess what! He said
Goku is on his way here!
To Namek!
And brace yourselves...
He'll be here in six days!
That's right! He's using a
replica of the Saiyan ship
he came to Earth
in as a baby!
My dad worked all day and
night to fix it up for him!
And he's still
training, too!
So he'll be ready to
take on the bad guys!
Whadda ya' think?
[GOHAN and KRILLIN giggling]
My dad's
coming here?
[GOHAN and KRILLIN laughing]
[ALL] Yeah!
[stuttering]
I don't believe it!
Goku! This means we still
have a fighting chance!
[GOKU grunting]
Gotta... Keep on...
Pushing the... limit!
[grunting continues]
[GOKU grunting]
[alarm beeping]
Hm? What? That's weird.
Has it been an hour already?
[beeping continues]
Come on!
How do you turn this
stupid thing off?
[beeping continues]
What the...
[DR. BRIEF] Hello!
Goku! Can you hear me?
Oh, It's you guys.
Did something happen
back on Earth?
No, everything's just
fine here. It's your ship!
Looks like you've sustained
a bit of damage to the hull.
[GOKU gasps]
[OOLONG] Hey there!
Probably just collided
with a small asteroid.
[GOKU] So, that's
a bad thing, right?
Well, it's
hard to say...
But if we don't get that
hull patched up, it will be!
[GOKU] So now what
are we supposed to do?!
You'll just have to
go outside and fix it.
Who, me?!
[DR. BRIEF] Sure!
Don't worry.
I had a custom fit space
suit prepared for you
in case of
emergency.
And there's
a repair box
stowed under the
front control panel,
complete with
special space glue.
'Kay, so I'm
in space...
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU screaming]
[DR. BRIEF] Relax, Goku.
Remember you're tethered
to the ship.
Just pull yourself in.
[thinking] Oh, right. So
that's what this thing's for.
Just gotta...
pull myself... in...
[GOKU screams]
Okay, this is bad!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU panting heavily]
Phew!
I gotta be
more careful...
[DR. BRIEF] Don't be
afraid to walk, Goku.
I installed magnets on
the feet of your spacesuit.
You did?
Wow! How 'bout that!
This'll sure
make things easier.
Hey, there it is.
[GOKU] Okay.
Let's see... Just a
little bit of space glue
and she'll be
good as new.
[DR. BRIEFS] Hm...
Looks like the impact
knocked the ship
a bit off course.
But as soon as I calculate
the new trajectory here...
[ALL gasp]
Oh no...
[GOKU] There.
That oughta' do it.
All better now.
Not a thing to worry about.
[DR. BRIEF] Goku! You've got
to get back inside the ship!
Something terrible
has happened!
The collision
with the asteroid
knocked your ship out of the
flight path I programmed,
and it's sent you
on a new trajectory
directly for
Alpha HZ.
It's a star
bigger than our sun.
You'll be incinerated
if you don't
get inside and
re-plot your course!
You have to hurry!
But, I don't know how
to reprogram the ship!
What the heck do I do?!
It's not difficult.
And I'll be here to talk
you through every step.
But only if you get to
the computer in time.
Right. I'm on my way.
[GOKU gasps]
Oh, come on! This is
definitely not good.
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU wailing]
This is crazy!
I just gotta think.
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU whimpering]
[DR. BRIEF] Goku! This is
no time to be standing around.
Yeah, I realize
that, but, uh...
You see, I uh... sorta
glued myself to the ship.
You did what?!
Now what
do I do?!
You guys got
any ideas?!
Goku!
Get outta there!
[GOKU grunting]
I don't mind a tan,
but this is ridiculous!
Sorry, but I'm not ready
to cash in just yet.
Kaa... Meeee...
Haa... Meeeee...
Haaa!
[GOKU] Phew! Wow!
Training under that heavy
gravity's really paying off!
Yay! Goku!
You did it!
[GOKU laughs]
Hmm?!
[GOKU squeals]
It's pulling
him back!
Oh, Goku...
[GOKU grunting]
'Kay... I'll try again.
But this time full power!
Kaaaa... Meeee...
Haaaaa... Meeee...
Haaaaaaaaaa!
[OOLONG] Ha-haa!
[PUAR] He made it! Yay!
I knew he could do it!
[DR. BRIEF] Mm-hmm!
It looks like
I'm finally safe.
Now if I can just figure
out how to get unstuck,
I'll be set!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA laughing]
I love it.
I should have learned
how to sense power levels
a long time ago!
There's a whole group
of them dead ahead.
A Namek village.
Just the sort of place I'd
expect to find a Dragon Ball!
[VEGETA laughing]
Frieza will
have to search
every inch of this
stinking planet!
But with my
newfound ability,
I'll always be one
step ahead of him!
[VEGETA laughing]
[VEGETA] Just
as I suspected...
Frieza hasn't
been here yet.
There's not a single
corpse to be seen!
Well, we'll see what
I can do about that.
Huh...?
Uh?
[NAMEK 1] It's an invader!
[NAMEK 2] What does he want?!
Which one of you
is the Elder?
I'm here for the Dragon Ball.
If you have it, get it.
How rude!
I am the Elder...
Now I must ask,
what use do you have
for the Dragon Ball?
That's my business,
old man. Where is it?
I'm sorry, but I cannot give
you what you are seeking.
Only those who are worthy
may claim the Dragon Ball.
Wrong answer...
[ALL gasp]
Bang.
[NAMEK 3] Elder!
[NAMEKS gasping]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[NARRATOR] After the day's
harrowing adventures,
Goku has resumed his
intensive training regimen.
But he still has
a long way to go...
He'll have to train at more
than twenty-times gravity
before he's ready
to face Vegeta!
Tune in next time,
as our heroes quest
for the Namekian Dragon
Balls continues...
On the next action-packed
episode of Dragon Ball Z!