[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
A mysterious stranger named
Trunks arrived from the future
with a warning for
Goku and his friends.
In three years time, an evil
scientist named Dr. Gero
will unleash two deadly
androids upon the Earth.
And if events leading up to
the attack are not changed,
the consequences will be
tragic for all of them.
Trunks left to fight the two
deadly androids in his own time,
leaving Goku and the others to
prepare themselves for the peril
that most certainly lie ahead.
It will require long hours
of training and discipline
to get their bodies
into the fighting shape
necessary to defeat
this unseen lethal foe.
But that's nothing new
to someone like Vegeta.
While the others
look toward a future
that has already been written,
Goku faces the daunting
task of leading them all
on a quest to change
the fate of the world.
Will they be ready to meet this
new Android threat head on?
Can Goku prevent Trunks' dark
predictions from coming to pass?
Only time will tell,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[YAMCHA grunts]
Come on, Yamcha! I know
you can go faster than that!
[thinking] That Vegeta.
He thinks he's so tough in
that little capsule of his,
training at 300 times gravity!
Well, I'll show him
that he's not half
as tough as he pretends to be!
I'll show him that I can
be just as tough as he is!
[YAMCHA] Let's take five, Puar.
I want to see what
Vegeta's up to in there.
[PUAR] I guess this is
what they mean by taking it
to the limit. Right, Yamcha?
[YAMCHA] Shh! Quiet, Puar,
and keep your head down!
[COMPUTER]
Initiate gravity simulation
300 times planet's
normal gravity.
[PUAR gasps]
[VEGETA grunts]
[COMPUTER] Initiating
defense program Level 5.
[VEGETA grunts]
[COMPUTER]
Assuming defense formation.
[VEGETA shouts]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA grunts]
[YAMCHA gasps]
[PUAR &amp; YAMCHA yell]
[VEGETA screams]
Uh-oh...
[YAMCHA] Whoa...
[VEGETA grunts]
[COMPUTER] Assuming defense
formation, Level maximum!
[VEGETA grunts]
[thinking] I can do this!
I am a Saiyan!
I am the most powerful
warrior in the universe!
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
[COMPUTER] Warning! System
overload! Error! Error! Error!
[YAMCHA] Boy, talk about your
radical training programs!
[DR. BRIEF] Well,
I guess it looks like
we'll be working a bit
late tonight, doesn't it, kitty?
[SCRATCH meows]
Thank you, Vegeta.
Hmm...
[BULMA snores]
[thinking] Whatever Vegeta
can take, I can take too!
[YAMCHA thinking]
300 times normal gravity
shouldn't be that tough!
I'm sure I can handle it...
[COMPUTER beeping]
[COMPUTER]
Initiate gravity simulation.
[YAMCHA grunts]
[thinking] Oh no!
What have I done?!
Maybe this wasn't such
a great idea after all!
[YAMCHA yells]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[thinking] I'll be
turned into a pancake
if I don't turn this thing off!
[thinking] Come on!
Just a little farther!
[COMPUTER]
Simulation terminated.
Normal gravity restored.
[BULMA hums]
[BULMA groans]
Everyone else is working so hard
to get ready for those androids
while I'm sitting around
the house doing nothing.
I wish there was
something I could do...
[MRS. BRIEF] Bulma!
I stopped by the bakery today
and look what I bought
for us! Nice, huh?
Don't these look scrumptious?
[MRS. BRIEF laughs]
Now, which one do you want?
They're all yours, Mom.
I'm not very hungry.
What? But Bulma,
what's wrong with you?
Are you feeling lonely
because all the boys are
spending all their time training
and not spending time with you?
That's it, isn't it, dear?
Oh, puh-lease!
I'm just not very hungry!
[DR. BRIEF yawns]
You know, I'm starting
to think Vegeta
is a few cards short
of a full deck.
Huh?
It wasn't enough to have
the simulator create
300 times gravity for him,
now he's demanding that
I make some more equipment
for him to train with.
And all he's going
to do is break it!
Somehow that doesn't
surprise me at all.
Well, I think it's great
he works so hard.
[DR. BRIEF] Oh sure,
he's training hard
but don't you think
he's over doing it a bit?
Oh no! I think
it's very admirable.
In my day, a man that showed
that much dedication to anything
was definitely husband material.
A girl would have to be crazy
to let him get away I tell you.
[MRS. BRIEFS slurps]
Oh my! What am I saying?
I'm a married woman!
--Huh?
--Hmm?
[VEGETA] I can do this!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA shouts]
[VEGETA yells]
[MRS. BRIEF screams]
[DR. BRIEF screams]
[BULMA] Vegeta!
I knew this would happen!
He's been trying to
do the impossible!
Where is he?
Vegeta?
[BULMA screams]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
[BOTH whimper]
You... okay...?
[VEGETA] Of course I am...
[VEGETA grunts]
--Huh?
[BULMA sighs]
How dare you! You dweeb!
You almost wrecked my house!
What are you trying to prove?!
[VEGETA grunts]
Wha--? Oh no! You're hurt!
Go! I don't need help!
I've got training to do!
You've got to stop
training for a while.
I mean look at you,
you're a complete wreck!
But I feel fine, I'm a Saiyan!
I can take a little pain.
It means nothing to me!
And I have to get
stronger than Kakarot!
Okay sure! We all know
you're a tough guy,
but you need to rest now!
I take orders from no one!
[VEGETA grunts]
Oh no!
[blasts firing]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOHAN grunts]
--Huh?!
--Wha...?!
Huh...?
He's gone!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOHAN] Huh...?
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[GOKU chuckles]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[GOHAN] Wow! They're moving so
fast I can't even see them!
That's it!
[GOHAN yells]
[BOTH] Huh?
[PICCOLO laughs]
[GOKU laughs]
Hey, Gohan! You're way too slow!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN growls]
[GOKU thinking] That's my boy!
[GOHAN yells]
[BULMA] Is he going
to be alright, Daddy?
[DR. BRIEF] I hope so!
The only thing he hasn't
bruised is his eyebrows.
If he stays in bed for a week
or so he should be alright!
He's dodged the bullet again.
It's a miracle he survived
such a horrible accident.
Those Saiyans are
practically indestructible!
[MRS. BRIEF sobs]
[MRS. BRIEF] Poor Vegeta!
Come on, Dear!
Let's let him rest.
[thinking] You Lunkhead...
[VEGETA] Kakarot...
I'll... get stronger,
Kakarot! I'll beat you!
[thinking]
He's having a bad dream.
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA gasps]
[GOKU chuckles]
Kakarot!
[VEGETA growls]
I'm stronger than you!
[VEGETA yells]
Hmm?
[VEGETA gasps]
It's you!
You're not a Saiyan!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA shouts]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] I am the strongest!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
They're too fast! I'll never
be able to catch up with them!
But I... I'm the one with
royal blood in my veins!
Father!
[KING VEGETA] Vegeta,
someday you will be
the strongest Saiyan
in the universe.
[VEGETA] Father?
[KING VEGETA] Those ships
are headed to distant galaxies.
From the day we are born,
we Saiyans are examined
for our power and leadership.
The weakest of our people
are sent to planets far away
where they face no
threat from our enemies!
Hmph!
Goodbye, pests!
Vegeta! You come from
a strong blood line
and you possess
the potential power
to join the super elite
of all Saiyans!
Never forget where you're from
and train very hard, my son!
Because if you have
proven yourself worthy,
perhaps someday you will
become a Super Saiyan!
[thinking] I haven't forgotten
what you said, Father!
I haven't forgotten my destiny!
And now I know that I will
be stronger than Kakarot!
[VEGETA] I am a Super Saiyan!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA] What is she doing here?
[COMPUTER]
Initiate gravity simulation.
400 times planet's
normal gravity.
Warning.
Simulation exceeds human
biological tolerance levels.
[VEGETA grunts]
[grunting continues]
[YAMCHA] Puar, It's time for
us to get back to work!
Yeah!
Stop it, Vegeta!
You are in no condition
to be doing this right now!
[BULMA] I know you don't
want to believe it,
but you are made
of flesh and blood!
Stop pestering me,
woman! Leave me alone!
[VEGETA yells]
You know I'm right!
So why don't you just
keep quiet and do as I say!
[VEGETA grunts]
Nothing to say?
Well, that's good!
Now go back to bed
and get some rest!
Not yet! I do have
something to say!
Huh? Uh... What?
Is something wrong?
Or maybe you're finally
going to apologize to me.
If that's the case,
then let's hear it!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
[BULMA gasps]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[NARRATOR] Goku and his friends
have only three short years
to prepare themselves
for the arrival
of Dr. Gero's evil androids.
And they plan to use
every minute of it!
But will these
powerful new enemies
still be too much
for them to handle?
Not if Vegeta has
anything to say about it.
On the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!