[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan stumbled upon
the discarded shell
of a mysterious creature,
the likes of which
he had never seen before!
But where in the world
did it come from?
...what hatched out of the shell
we found in the time capsule.
Right. It grew up and
then molted out of its skin...
you think?
It's still wet...
This thing must be
somewhere close.
[NARRATOR] This vile
monstrosity is on the loose,
lurking about the countryside.
But did it really
come from the future?
And for what sinister purpose?
While Trunks and the others
contemplate the answers
to these questions,
elsewhere, trouble is afoot!
[NARRATOR] It's the Androids!
And their quest to find
Goku is almost complete.
Meanwhile,
Kami looked on in horror
as the tensions built
on the earth below.
A terrible new evil
is about to be unleashed!
It there anyone
who can stop it?
Find out today!
[GOHAN] Hey, Trunks...
[GOHAN] Earth to Trunks!
Huh? Yeah?!
[GOHAN] Do you have any idea
what kind of a creature
that might have been back there?
Nope. Afraid not.
But whatever it was,
it was just about
the ugliest thing
that I've ever seen!
[GOHAN]
Man, you're not kidding!
That thing almost
made me sick to my stomach!
--[TRUNKS chuckles]
--[GOHAN] Yuck!
[GOHAN] Hey, you said that
it probably got here
four years ago, right?
[TRUNKS] Yeah. At least
that's what the indicator
in the time capsule read before
the batteries went dead. Why?
[GOHAN] I just find it
hard to believe that
a creature like that could
be here for four whole years
without anyone noticing it!
I mean, doesn't that seem
a little bit weird to you?
Yeah.
But what I want to know is...
who sent it here
and for what reason?
[birds chripping]
[thinking] Really...
How long does it take her
to pick out
a new dress, anyway?
So this is the best
outfit in your store?
Yup! You won't find
better n' that, li'l lady!
[ANDROID 18] Hmph!
Well... now how do you like it?
[ANDROID 18]
How do you think I like it?
It's grotesque!
But I guess I can't expect
to find much better
in a hick town like this.
[ANDROID 18] It'll just
have to do. Take care, now.
Hey! You can't leave
here without paying?!
[ANDROID 18] Whatever.
[CLERK] Hey...!
Why... you...!
Huh?!
[CLERK]
Hey! Ya'll come back now!
Shoot... Crazy hippies...
[phone dials]
[CLERK] Yeah, hello, sheriff?
I got trouble!
I've just been robbed by
a bunch of weirdos in a van!
[police sirens]
We've got company.
Maybe I should say hello.
[sirens continue]
Huh?
[TROOPER 1 and 2 yell]
[yells]
[groans]
[BOTH groan]
Walter... What just happened?
[music plays from radio]
[TV REPORTER A] And now,
Channel 8's continuing coverage
of the disaster in Gingertown...
To recap the situation,
all activities in the
West City suburb of Gingertown
came to a screeching
halt this morning
when the entire population
mysteriously vanished
into thin air.
Authorities are at a loss to
explain the sudden disappearance
of Gingertown's inhabitants,
and attempts at contacting
anyone within the city itself
have so far gone unanswered.
Gingertown, huh?
We'll bring you
the latest reports "live"
as we investigate
the "Crisis in Gingertown."
[gasps]
Gingertown isn't far from where
we found the time machine.
Hmm... I wonder...
[phone ringing]
Yo, Krillin here.
[BULMA] Krillin, this Bulma!
Did Gohan and Trunks
show up there yet?
No, no sign
of them so far...
So... What's up...?
Uh, you sound
all wigged out Bulma.
Listen, Krillin.
Turn your TV on to Channel 8.
And hurry, because there's
something on right now
that I think you guys are
really gonna want to see...
[KRILLIN] What's the big deal?
I thought they were
just showing reruns.
Just do it, ya dip!
--[KRILLIN] All right...
--[YAMCHA] Hey, Krillin,
who's on the phone?
It's Bulma.
She wants us to...
watch something on TV...
Why? Is she
gonna be on a show?
Yeah, and now she
wants us to watch
so she can brag about
how famous she is!
[laughs] Probably...
Well... it looks like
we have more details
on the "Crisis in Gingertown."
Our latest reports
indicate that there are
no signs of life anywhere.
However, it seems the
clothing of the victims
has been discovered
throughout the city...
[TV REPORTER B]
Wait! Our Channel 8 reporter
has just arrived
at the scene...!
What... is goin'... on?!
Ah... I'm reporting "live" from
downtown Gingertown
and the entire place
is completely deserted!
All of the 15,000 residents
have suddenly... disappeared!
Fifteen thousand...?
Piles of garments lie
scattered throughout the city,
as though these people were
sucked right
out of their clothes!
[TV REPORTER C]
There are also indications that
these people may have been
trying to defend themselves
against someone...
--[TV REPORTER C] or something!
--[ROSHI] Oh...
Goodness!
Man. This is really bad!
It's... the Androids!
They must've done this!
I doubt that...
Huh?
And I've got a feeling
that Gohan and Trunks
are going to agree with me.
Wait a minute.
Don't tell me this has
something to do with that
other time machine you found!
That's getting a little
too weird for me!
[BULMA] Well, weird or not,
Krillin, I know it's true!
When Gohan and Trunks show up,
tell them what
I've told you, all right?
[KRILLIN] You got it.
Well, it looks like
Goku's sound asleep.
And guys,
he's looking much better!
Huh?
[GOHAN]
Hello...! Master Roshi!
Is anyone home?
[GOHAN] Huh?
Ah, Krillin...
What's going on?
[KRILLIN] Gohan, Trunks...
C'mon over here and have a look
at what's on the news!
What'd ya mean?
[distant screaming]
Oh the humanity!
As you can hear, the city's
not deserted after all!
[distant gunfire and screaming]
[TV REPORTER C]
Now I can hear shots!
It sounds like
machine gun fire coming from
the very core of the city!
But I can't make out
who's doing the shooting!
[distant gunfire continues]
And the commotion appears to
have calmed down once again...
[yells]
[ALL] Huh?
[stammers, yells]
Huh?
[quavered groans]
What is it?
Tell me what's
happening down there!
Yes. Please tell us.
It's awful...
Even worse than I feared!
What...? What do you mean?!
[PICCOLO] You're not making
any sense! Explain yourself!
What... happened?
Krillin, quick!
Flip it to another channel!
[KRILLIN] Right...
[beeping]
[gunfire on TV]
--[YAMCHA gasps]
--[ROSHI] Hm?
It... sounds like it's over...
[groans]
[PICCOLO] You old fool!
You actually enjoy keeping me
in suspense like this,
don't you?!
[PICCOLO]
I want you to tell me
exactly what's
going on down there!
Start talkling!
Well...?
No... I won't...
[PICCOLO] Look, old man,
I have no intention
on asking you again.
Now I need to know
what's happening on Earth!
Yes, but... telling you
is pointless... now.
[PICCOLO] What?! Why?!
Because when
you and I become one,
you will know for yourself
everything that's happened.
Huh?
No... Kami...!
So you've finally
come to your senses.
I was beginning to wonder how
much longer I'd have to wait.
[KAMI] We must hurry...
before there are
any more victims on Earth!
[PICCOLO] I'm ready! But let's
get one thing straight.
When we combine,
we use my body. Understand?
Agreed. It will be so.
Your body is much younger and
more powerful. I understand.
[chuckles]
Our union will make you
more powerful, Piccolo.
And you will
obtain my vast knowledge.
[KAMI] I hope you will
use these new powers wisely.
[KAMI sighs]
[gasps]
For our merger to transpire,
place your hand on my chest.
Yes.
Aah! No, Kami, no!
[KAMI] There's nothing
to worry about, Mr. Popo.
[gasps]
[KAMI] Alone, I can do little
to help those on Earth.
The time is right.
[whimpers]
Piccolo has changed.
The evil that once
filled his entire being
has greatly diminished.
[KAMI] And when we unite,
I trust he will use
our combined strength
in the service of good.
No, please...
I thank you
for all you've done...
Mr. Popo.
No... Kami, don't...!
♪
[yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
[KAMI yells]
[KAMI continues yelling]
[PICCOLO grunts, groans]
[PICCOLO yells]
[POPO sobs]
[gasps]
Good-bye Kami. I'll miss you.
Please be careful...
No longer am I
Kami or Piccolo.
I am the Namek who has
long since forgotten his name.
I... must go...
[KORIN] Good-bye, old friend.
♪
[snoring]
We are still attempting
to re-connect "live"
via satellite with our
correspondent in Gingertown,
but at last word
it looks like he too
may have become a victim.
So... it's some kind of creature
that's causing
all the trouble?
Yeah, right.
We found it's shell...
near the time capsule.
[ROSHI] Mmm...
Now... I've got
to go to Gingertown!
[YAMCHA] No!
[KRILLIN] You can't, Trunks!
[TRUNKS] Hey, don't worry
about me. I'll be all right.
After all, I am a Super Saiyan.
And besides, it's the Androids
we really have to worry about.
[KRILLIN]
Huh? Are you sure?
[GOHAN] I'll go with you!
--[CHICHI] What?!
--[KRILLIN] Huh?
Oh no you're not!
I think you're forgetting
about your father!
He's more important
than some dumb creature!
But Mom...
If Trunks has to fight
he might need my help!
Enough! You're not
going anywhere, young man!
You're staying right here!
No, I'm going.
--[KRILLIN] Uuuh...
--YAMCHA gasps]
[TRUNKS] Sorry kid,
but I'm going solo.
Do what your mother says.
They need you here
to help protect your father
in case the Androids show up.
It's the right thing
to do, Gohan. Trust me.
All right. I'll stay then.
Hey, Trunks! Check it out...
but if things look dicey,
you get back here!
Yeah... he's right.
Now, don't try
anything foolish out there
because we need you to
help us fight the Androids!
Hey, don't worry about me.
[wheezing]
Hm?
[clickling sound]
[footsteps]
[CREATURE growling lowly]
[CREATURE wheezing]
At last we meet...
face to face...
[CREATURE growls lowly]
[chuckles]
[CREATURE growls]
[NARRATOR] Piccolo stares
into the face of evil!
Are the mighty Namek's
new powers enough
to hold this
formidable foe at bay?
So far, this sinister creature
has wiped out an entire city,
and he has no intention
of stopping there...!
On the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!