[GOKU]
I'd better get moving...
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku was running
down Snake Way,
hoping to get some special
martial arts training
from the legendary
King Kai...
Meanwhile Gohan was busy
with his own survival
training back on Earth.
And the young
Saiyan soon learned
that it's not easy when you're
out in the world all alone.
Friends are hard
to hold on to,
especially when
they're the main course
on the menu for
a hungry T-Rex!
Careful Gohan, or you could
end up being his dessert!
Luckily, Gohan's a
natural born fighter,
just like his
father Goku.
But he hasn't developed
the fighting skills
of his father yet.
And with his dino buddy
digested by the big T-Rex,
Gohan soon found out,
only the strong survive!
Speaking of strong...
Two sinister Saiyans are headed
towards Earth right now.
Every minute
they get closer
and that means
it won't be long
before we all find out what
the big bang theory really is...
Keep your eyes on the skies and
get ready for Dragon Ball Z!
[birds chirp]
[squawking]
[snoring]
[DINOSAURS squawk]
Hm? Breakfast time!
[GOHAN giggles]
[giggling continues]
Haaaaaa!
Ahh...
[chuckles]
[loud thuds]
Huh?
[growling]
What's up? Nice day,
huh? You look hungry!
[roars]
[GOHAN]
Whoa!
[roars]
[roaring continues]
Catch me if you can!
Nyah! Nyah!
Great! It looks like
tail steak for breakfast!
Hey... You won't have much of
a tail if you keep this up.
I used to have a
tail too, you know!
[T-REX groans]
So, he's starting to
master the training.
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Somewhere, deep
in the vastness of space,
the two Saiyan warriors
continue their journey
towards planet Earth.
[COMPUTER]
Prince Vegeta!
We are now within one
parsec of the planet Arlia.
Initiating
vapor bath.
It is time to
wake up now!
[beeping]
[YAMCHA] Oh boy!
I can't believe Kami
is going to train me!
I'm so excited I can hardly
wait to get started!
Just take it easy, Yamcha.
You know we
have to find out
where Tien and
Chiaotzu are first!
[KRILLIN laughs]
I bet they'll be surprised
to see us! Heh, heh!
And once we
find those two,
Yamcha can start his
training with Kami
and then no one will be
able to beat him in battle!
That's right...
I'll be ready for anything!
[KRILLIN and PUAR laugh]
[PUAR] You said it!
That'll be great!
[YAMCHA] Hey, step on it,
would ya, Bulma?!
[VEGETA] Nappa? Nappa?
Are you awake?
[NAPPA groans]
I am now.
What's going on?
Nothing much.
But, I thought we'd make a stop
and stretch our legs a bit.
Get some exercise.
[VEGETA] Planet Arlia's
not far from here.
Maybe we can sell it
for a nice price.
That sounds good.
[chuckles]
I hope these Arlians
know how to fight,
we haven't had any
real competition
in a very long time.
Wow, whatta mess!
[VEGETA] Huh?
[NAPPA] There's not much
to this place is there?
[VEGETA] Obviously not.
Let's have a look
around shall we?
Are you sure you can get a
high price for this planet?
Doubt it...
[VEGETA] Let's check
around a little more.
[beeping]
[ARLIAN 1] You are trespassing
on Arlian territory!
[ARLIAN 2] Make one move
and we'll blast ya!
It was a good day to
go hunting after all!
[ARLIAN 1] Let's give
them a proper welcoming.
[ARLIAN 1 chuckles]
[NAPPA]
Let's blast 'em!
Easy!
[ARLIAN 1] Surrender peacefully
or face the consequences!
No!
[ARLIAN 1]
Have it your way then.
You've left us no choice!
Prepare to be destroyed!
Hyaah!
[ARLIAN 1]
That's the end of them!
[gasps]
[ARLIAN 2]
Surrender at once!
Yeah, make me! Grrrh!
[VEGETA telepathically]
Nappa!
Surrender to them! Let's have
a little fun while we're here!
[NAPPA]
Oh, alright...
[ARLIAN 1] Move in!
They're giving up!
[ARLIAN 2] Ha! I guess
we were too much for them!
[ARLIAN 1]
Eh, they sure are ugly!
[ARLIAN 2] But they'll be good
entertainment for the King.
[NAPPA chuckles]
[sirens blare]
[POLICEMAN A]
Stop thief! Stop!
[POLICEMAN B]
You're under arrest!
[LAUNCH]
Ugh! Get off my back!
Sorry for all
the trouble,
but this oughta give you
some bang for your bucks!
[POLICEMEN yell]
[screaming]
Well, this is
for you, Tien!
And you better
wait for me,
'cause I'm gonna get
you lots of food
with these
greenbacks!
[ATTENDANT]
More fruit, your highness?
[KING]
Most entertaining!
Come Lemlia,
won't you join me?
[PRISONERS groan]
[ARLIAN GUARD]
Get in there, ugly!
You'll be
glad to know,
your cell doesn't
have any rats!
The prisoners ate 'em all!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Hey remind me to
get that guy, okay?
[VEGETA chuckles]
[PRISONER 1]
Look at those aliens!
[PRISONER 2] Goodness, they're
an ugly pair, aren't they?
[PRISONER 3] Maybe they think
that we're the ugly ones!
Did you ever
think of that?
[PRISONER 2]
Hmph! Speak for yourself!
[ATLA] Be quiet,
all of you!
It doesn't matter
what they look like!
They're stuck in here
just like the rest of us!
Can't you see that?
They're just more victims
of that tyrant king!
Locked away
and left to rot!
I'm afraid you visitors
have come at a bad time.
The new king of Arlia
is very ruthless.
He uses us prisoners
for his own amusement.
He even went so far as to
steal my wife, Lemlia,
on the day that
we were to be married...
So you can imagine
the pain I feel.
[KING] Lemlia please,
you have to eat something.
[LEMLIA] No thank you.
I'm not hungry.
[KING]
Don't be so stubborn...
You have to put the
past behind you...
You are my Queen now.
[LEMLIA] No! There is only
one that I truly love.
[FIGHTER 2 yells and groans]
[KING]
Enough!
Take Gregor to the pit!
Esaw is the new champion!
[GREGOR]
No, not the pit!
Please, Sire, not the pit! No!
This isn't fair!
[GREGOR screams]
No! Please.
Don't leave me down here!
Give me another chance!
[GREGOR screams]
No, Yeddy!
Please, stay away from me!
Stay away! A-Ahhh!
[GREGOR screams]
[KING sighs]
[KING] I'm suffering
from royal boredom!
[ATTENDANT] Sire, earlier
today we captured two aliens.
They're in
the dungeon now!
[KING]
Aliens?
Have the guards bring them
to the arena immediately.
Maybe they can provide some
entertainment fit for a king!
[VEGETA] Don't put yourselves
out! We're already here!
[KING] What's the
meaning of this?
Why don't these prisoners have
an armed escort in my chamber?
[ATTENDANT]
I don't know, Sire!
No orders were even
sent to the dungeon.
[VEGETA] Your guards met with
an unfortunate accident.
[ATLA] Now's my chance to
get out of this place.
[PRISONERS groan]
[ATLA] I must to get to
the King's chamber at once!
Amazing!
Those two aliens melted
through the cell bars.
That makes things a
lot easier for me!
[KING] How dare you!
Soon it will be your turn
to meet with an
unfortunate accident.
You may not want to
watch this, my dear.
[LEMLIA]
Very well.
[KING] I'll see that my
guards make short work
of these
repulsive creatures!
Really?
[KING]
Ah, let's see!
Yes, we'll test the big
one with the shiny head
against our
champion in combat!
We'll save the
little one for last,
he won't put up much of
a fight I'm sure!
Now teach
them a lesson!
[ESAW] Yes, Sire!
[KING]
And Esaw?
I'll see that you
retire a wealthy man
if you can defeat
both of them.
Now begin!
[ESAW] Haa!
[ESAW yowls]
[KING] Huh?!
[ESAW screams]
[NAPPA] Heh! I guess that makes
you the new champion, Vegeta!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[KING]
Not bad!
But ten of our finest warriors
have mastered techniques
using energy
just like yours!
They have? Interesting!
We'd like to fight them!
Ready?
[KING] I'll see you suffer
for your insolence!
[NAPPA] Yeah, whatever.
Can we get on with this already?
[KING]
Ah! How dare you!
C'mon, your
heinousness!
Bring on that cricket brigade
of yours! We're ready!
[KING] Take a good look
at my Elite Royal Guards.
Now, you won't be talking
so tough, will you?
[ROYAL GUARD 1]
Fire!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Was that it? It felt good.
Real refreshing!
[KING]
Oh, I'll make you pay!
If you think you can
just walk out of here,
you are sadly
mistaken!
Guards attack!
Destroy them!
[ROYAL GUARD 3]
We got 'em now!
[ROYAL GUARD 6]
Attack!
[NAPPA laughs]
[ROYAL GUARDS yell]
[GOKU thinking]
Where's King Kai's place?
It's got to be around
here somewhere!
[NAPPA yells]
[ROYAL GUARDS whimper]
[KING] Release Yeddy!
Release Yeddy!
Hurry before it's too late!
[rumbling]
[YEDDY growls gutturally]
So, it's the old giant
bug in the ground trick!
[KING] Yeddy,
destroy these creatures!
They're bad!
Very, very bad!
We're bad?
Well, a little.
[VEGETA] Over here!
[NAPPA] Hey, ugly!
[NAPPA grunts]
[KING] That fool! He's no
match for Yeddy's strength!
[NAPPA grunts]
[YEDDY roars]
[KING] No!
Hey! I've got one more
little surprise for you!
[NAPPA grunts]
Yaah! It's your
going away present!
[KING]
No! Impossible!
Coward!
[KING] Please!
Don't hurt me!
Aaahh!
[ATLA] It sounds like there's
a battle going on up there!
I'm coming for
you, Lemlia.
What? Unbelievable!
The king and his Royal
Guard have been destroyed!
[VEGETA]
Computer.
[COMPUTER]
Yes, Prince Vegeta?
[VEGETA]
Send the pods at once.
[COMPUTER]
Initiating retrieval sequence.
[ATLA] Do you two realize
what you have done?
You have freed our planet
from centuries of bondage!
At last Arlia is a place where
a new beginning can be made!
From now on you two
visitors from space
will be known as heroes
among our people.
I can't begin to tell you
how very grateful I am.
[ATLA]
Farewell, my friends!
You will always be
welcome here on Arlia!
[ATLA] Thank you!
We will never forget you!
[LEMLIA] Atla?
[ATLA] Huh?
[LEMLIA] Atla! Thank goodness!
You're alive!
[ATLA] Do my eyes deceive me?
Is it really you, Lemlia?
[LEMLIA] Yes, it's me,
Altla, your Lemlia!
[ATLA] You don't know how happy
I am to see you, my love!
[VEGETA]
Let's go, Nappa!
We couldn't give away
this place if we wanted to.
[NAPPA] But that thing back
there said we were heroes!
Being a hero is
highly overrated.
Ergh. Too bad, I guess, that
was a big waste of time then.
[VEGETA] Don't worry there's
still Earth to conquer!
[LEMLIA] Atla!
[VEGETA] Hold on. I've got
some unfinished business
to take care of...
This planet has a
serious bug problem.
[ATLA]
Lemlia, my darling!
[LEMLIA]
Atla!
[giggles]
[LEMLIA]
Atla, my love!
[ATLA] My darling! At last
we can be together forever!
[LEMLIA and ATLA giggle]
There's nothing like
a little fireworks
when you say goodbye!
[NAPPA] Heh! Their moon, too!
Nice touch!
[VEGETA] I think we've
made the universe
a cleaner
place today.
Arlia deserved
what they got.
I just hope Earth is a lot
better than that planet.
It will be...
Earth has the Dragon Balls.
Once we find them, we can
wish for whatever we want!
Hm. Immortality,
here we come!
[evil laughing]
[NARRATOR] The dangerous
duo is on a mission
and they've got Earth
in their sights.
What the world needs
now is a hero,
someone to
save the day.
Someone like Goku, but he's
still busy on Snake Way.
[GOKU] Doesn't this
road ever end?!
[NARRATOR]
We'll find out...
on the next
exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!