[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragonball Z,
the battle between
Captain Ginyu,
leader of the Ginyu Force,
and Goku began!
[NARRATOR] In an effort
to test his own strength,
Captain Ginyu tried to get
Goku to reveal his true power,
but the Saiyan would not play
Ginyu's game, at first...
Now, let's go!
[NARRATOR] But as Goku
increased his power level,
Ginyu began to
reconsider his strategy.
Ahh... No way!
[NARRATOR] Does the
captain of the Ginyu Force
stand a chance
against Goku?
Find out today!
[JEICE thinking] Man o' man!
Now I see what Burtur and
I were really up against!
We didn't have a clue!
undred  housand!
Fighting power one
and seventeen
Oh no!
That's only three thousand away
from Captain Ginyu's maximum!
[GOKU growling]
What?! Darn! No way!
Hey! Hey, stop that!
[GOKU shouting]
[GOKU] Actually, I'm
just getting warmed up!
[GINYU] Oh, a wise guy,
huh?! Now, let's see here!
What?! One hundred
and forty thousand!
No! It can't be!
[GOKU] I think your friend's
having a nervous breakdown!
[JEICE] He's just
cooling off, mate!
He'll be back!
[GINYU yelling]
[GOKU growling]
One hundred and fifty
thousand! Unreal!
[growling continues]
[GOKU shouts]
Jeice! Look out!
[GINYU grunts]
[JEICE] Whoa!
[GINYU laughs]
[GINYU gasps]
Here! Try these
on for size!
[JEICE] Watch it!
[JEICE] Captain! I think it'd be
wise if we left and got Frieza!
[GINYU] Shut up, Jeice,
I'm in charge here!
[GOKU yells]
Wha--? Huuuuuuh?!
[GINYU] So this is the real you!
undred a housand!
One
eighty
Astounding! Incredible!
Man, we should
be getting
the heck out of
here right now!
Yeah, I've seen about
all I want to see!
There's no need
to be scared of me!
Just say you're sorry
for what you've done
and leave and no harm
will come to you!
What? Apologize?!
[GOKU] That's right!
[GINYU] We're the Ginyu Force!
We-We never apologize!
Uhh.
[GOKU] I'm sorry to hear that!
[GINYU] You don't scare me!
We don't bow to anybody,
not even a guy like you!
Although, I must admit...
we've never really
faced anyone like you!
[GINYU wails]
[BULMA] Huh?!
Oh, my gosh! What happened?!
This is horrible!
Man...
Hmm...
[BULMA] I had no idea
it was this bad!
This is just awful!
How could anyone do
this to these people
just for the Dragon Balls?
It doesn't make sense.
Man...
Gosh, and here I was
thinking I had it bad...
[BULMA] Oh, you poor
little guy. Ooh...
Oh, Goku,
hurry up!
We need you!
[GURU] What are you
looking for, Dende?
[DENDE] I was hoping that
Nail would come back, Guru.
[GURU] Try looking
below, to your left.
[DENDE] It's him!
Guru, Nail's come back!
[GURU] Who is it, Dende?
I can not see very well.
[DENDE] It's Nail, Guru!
Nail's come back.
[GURU] It couldn't be Nail!
I sent him on a mission.
[NAIL] It is I, Guru.
Nail, why have
you returned?
I asked you to help
the Earthlings,
can't you respect an old man's
wishes even in his last hour?
[NAIL] I know
what's coming, Guru.
And you do too.
You also know that
I can't be anywhere
except by your side
at this time!
[GURU] There's nothing
you can do, my son.
You know that.
[NAIL] But, Guru,
I have to try!
[GURU] But you can't succeed.
[NAIL] Then I'll die trying!
[GURU] Nail!
Mmm. You're a fine young man.
Hmm...
Isn't that the
place over there?
[KRILLIN] I don't know,
it all looks the same to me.
[KRILLIN] Hey, you
were right, Gohan!
This is it!
We better hurry!
[KRILLIN] Where is she?
Uhh, Bulma, where are you?
Come out, come out
wherever you are!
Hm, I guess
she's not here.
Hey, Bulma!
Well... Huh.
[KRILLIN] Keep your eyes open
for the Dragon Radar, Gohan.
[KRILLIN] Maybe a mountain lion
drug her into this little cave!
[GOHAN] I wouldn't want
to be the mountain lion!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, I
guess you're right.
Oh, brother!
I can't believe it.
You leave a girl stranded
in the middle of nowhere,
and she's still gone
when you need her.
[GOHAN] Hey, Krillin.
Check this out.
[KRILLIN] Oh, yeah. Wow.
Some sort of hieroglyphics, huh?
ki!
No, silly! This is a track
from Bulma's air
She took off somewhere!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Oh, great, a ruthless
killer is about to find
the key to immortality and
she's out cruisin' somewhere!
Bad timing, huh?
C'mon, Gohan!
We've got to find her!
Without the Dragon Radar,
this is hopeless!
[FRIEZA] Oh, and what
do we have here?
Well, well, well...
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Well, I guess it's time for you
to get going, my little brother.
I know you can do it!
[GURU] Come here, boy.
[DENDE] Yes, Guru
[DENDE] Yes, Sir?
[GURU] I have a gift for you
to help you on your mission.
[GURU grunts]
[DENDE whimpers softly]
[GURU] It's okay, Dende.
Don't be scared
of this new power
that you feel
within you, son.
It has always existed inside
of you, I merely uncovered it.
Must I go?
[GURU] The sooner,
the better, my son.
Goodbye, Guru!
Please take care of yourself
while I'm gone, okay?
[GURU] Be strong,
my little warrior.
It pleases me that
in these dark hours,
a flame so small
burns brightly.
[GINYU] Of course,
I know what you are now!
You're not an ordinary Saiyan,
you're a-a... a Super Saiyan!
Huh?!
Call me what you want,
it doesn't matter to me.
Because the outcome is
still going to be the same!
This is what Frieza
was afraid of,
this is why he destroyed
the planet Vegeta!
[GINYU] Aargh! Why me?!
Rrgh! I am the
great Captain Ginyu!
[JEICE] That's it, Captain!
Remember who you are!
Sir! He's making you
lose your composure
and forget about style!
Don't let him do it!
[GOKU] My offer still stands!
We don't have to fight!
[GINYU] Hmm...?
[GOKU] You can still choose
to admit you're wrong
and leave this place!
Alright!
One way or the other,
let's settle this right now!
It's your choice!
You're serious,
aren't you!
You'd let us go? We
could leave just like that?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, why not?
You're the ones
who will suffer most
for what you've done
to these people.
It's bad karma!
Bad karma?
[GOKU] That's right!
You'll have to reap
what you've sown.
[GINYU thinking] Wait a second.
Something's not right here!
Super Saiyans are supposed
to be radically efficient
killing machines. But this
guy is as gentle as a lamb!
He must not be a fully
developed Super Saiyan,
which means he still
has weaknesses!
And I think I
just figured out
what this guy's
greatest weakness is!
Yeah. Yeah! Yeeaah!
I thought I was
dealing with a lion here
but now I realize you're
just a pussycat!
Huh?
[GINYU] You heard me!
Ha ha ha!
Yes, my friend!
It's hard to win fights when
you're way too forgiving.
[GINYU] And I know you
wouldn't even hurt a fly
if you didn't have
to, would you?
[GINYU chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Oh, to sip from
the cup of eternity,
and fly free on wings
of immortality!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[DENDE] Hm?!
[FRIEZA] Hmm?
It's just a brat.
Kids are learning to fly
so young these days.
[GURU] The evil one
has arrived, Nail.
[NAIL] Yes, Guru.
I feel his presence.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Hello,
is anybody home?
[NAIL] Yes, I'm home.
Welcome, "friend".
[FRIEZA] Why,
thank you very much.
I'm a visitor here,
touring your lovely planet
and I happened to find
seven Dragon Balls!
A man at the gift shop
told me about
the legend behind the
balls; about the wish.
[FRIEZA] But the balls don't
work unless you have a password.
Would you happen to know
the password, my good man?
Not me.
You should check with the
Chamber of Commerce, "friend".
They have that sort
of information.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] The Chamber is dead...
And so are you if you
don't tell me the password.
[scouter beeping]
[FRIEZA] Hmm?
Hm...
Huh?!
Well, well. Friends
of yours, I presume?
I hope you boys don't plan
on ganging up on me now.
That wouldn't be fair!
Four strong men
against just one of me.
Go back...
[FRIEZA] Hm...
Hmph.
So, we arrived
just in time!
[NAIL growls]
Look! I can handle
this! It'd be better
if you guys took off!
Oh, I get it, Nail.
You want all the glory
for yourself, huh?
Well, forget it!
He destroyed our village!
This guy is ours.
Bald and bold, heh!
[FRIEZA] Oh, my!
[FRIEZA] Goodness!
Well, I don't want to
burst your bubble, boys.
But, you have the fighting
power of a boy's scout troop!
We can play if you'd like,
but it will be your last game!
[growling]
I've heard enough!
Guys, wait!
Please, listen!
You don't have--
Don't worry
about us, Nail!
Just take care of Guru!
[GURU grunts]
[GURU] My children...
Raah!
Haaah!
Rrgh!
[yelling]
[WARRIORS screaming]
[screaming continues]
[WARRIOR B grunting]
[WARRIOR C yelling]
[WARRIOR A yelling]
[WARRIOR A gurgling]
My dear man, do you
know the password
which activates
the Dragon Balls?
[grunting]
[wheezing]
Well, do you?
[FRIEZA] I can't hear you.
Perhaps if I let go?
There!
[FRIEZA] Fool!
[NAIL] No!
oy?
[FRIEZA] Why so blue,
lizard
You look so stressed,
but everything's fine!
Just tell me the password.
It's that simple.
Or... your friend could tell.
Would you rather have me
extract the information
from your friend?
Look! My friend
is very old.
He's dying as it is, and
he doesn't need your help!
You wouldn't
harm him anyway!
Think about it:
If he dies than you can't
use the Dragon Balls
because he created
the Dragon Balls.
And when he goes, they
go with him, got it?
Ohh...
Besides, look; he's
a very sensitive person.
He's spent his whole life
healing and teaching our people.
On this planet, he's a prophet!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA] A holy man? Well,
I must introduce myself.
I, too, am revered by people
all over the Universe!
Hm...
Aah...
[FRIEZA] Hello, there.
Nice to meet you.
My, my, he's not much of
a conversationalist, huh?
[FRIEZA] Yoo-hoo! Are you mad
at me because I didn't knock?
How rude!
Maybe you'd speak
up if your friend here
was crying out in pain?
Whatd'ya think?!
I think you would be the
one crying out in pain
if you fought him.
He's not like the other Nameks
that you've fought so far.
He's been fully trained
in the Ancient Way!
Pure-hearted warriors always
rise to a new level of strength
when forced to defend
themselves against
the vile sort of darkness
that you represent!
[FRIEZA] Listen here,
you Green Blob!
Watch your mouth!
[VEGETA growls]
[GURU using telepathy] Nail,
we must buy as much time
as we can for the Earthlings!
[NAIL using telepathy]
Yes, Guru!
[FRIEZA] Alright, old man!
[FRIEZA growls]
You obviously don't like
to exchange pleasantries.
Very well, then, let's cut
straight to the chase, shall we?
What's the password?
[JEICE] That's it, Captain!
You're looking good, mate!
eter!
I'd say you're back to a full
"ten" on the style
[GINYU] Yes, style! That's
us, the mighty Ginyu Force!
We're professionals!
For us, killing is
just part of the job!
But it's not like that
for you, is it?
[GINYU chuckles]
You can't beat us!
[laughing]
[NARRATOR] Has Captain Ginyu
exposed Goku's only weakness?
Does the Saiyan from
Earth have what it takes
to defeat the Ginyu Force?
Tune in next time
for Dragon Ball Z!