[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Krillin met with
a terrible fate,
much to the horror
of his companions.
[NARRATOR] Krillin was
then flung mercilessly
below to a watery grave
by the evil, super-giant.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[NARRATOR] While Gohan
was left alone
to defend his friend's honor,
Dende recovered Krillin
from the depths of the sea.
Kid, no! Move! Look out!
[NARRATOR] The young Gohan
made an incredible stand
against Frieza, but his valiant
efforts would eventually crumble
under the weight of
Frieza's enormous power.
Bye-bye... Brat!
[GOHAN screams]
[NARRATOR] Is there
any hope left
for the courageous,
little warrior
when even Vegeta seems too
scared to lend a hand?
[NARRATOR] Find out today!
[GOHAN groans]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[skull crackling]
[GOHAN screams]
Poor boy! Vegeta, how can
you be so cold-hearted?
Can't you see that
the boy is in pain?
I guess you're just too
petrified to help him,
aren't you?
[FRIEZA laughs]
What a shame. He was
such a brave little kid.
Too bad! It's hard to find
good friends in this world.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOHAN groans]
[VEGETA] Even if I managed
get Frieza off of him,
the kid's still finished.
It'd be better if he was
just put out of his misery.
[GOHAN groans]
[FRIEZA] There, there.
It will all be over soon.
[GOKU thinking] Uh-oh!
Somebody's energy signal
is disappearing!
Whoever it is
is in deep trouble!
What? It's Gohan! I need
to get out of this thing!
[GOKU thinking] It's no use!
I've got to stay
here a little longer
or I won't be able
to help him anyway!
[GOKU thinking]
Hang in there, son!
Please!
Uh-oh! Gohan's energy
signal is fading!
I'm not gonna let it happen!
We've been through
too much together...
[PICCOLO] You were just a
pampered kid when I took you in.
But you never gave up.
You never failed to
surprise me either.
[PICCOLO] Maybe I shouldn't
have been so hard on you...
But you took it
without complaint...
And I could tell that despite
the hardship I put you through,
you truly cared about me...
So I died for you.
[PICCOLO] And I'd do
it all over again.
Gohan, it feels good
knowing that I've helped
my only true friend...
[GOHAN] No, Piccolo! No!
I'm almost there!
Don't you let go!
[GOHAN groans]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Why can't I stomach this?
I've seen much worse than
this without blinking an eye.
[GOKU thinking]
Okay, this is it!
Healed or not, I've got
to try to help Gohan!
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Sayonara, kid!
[VOICE] Destructo Disk!
Huh?!
[FRIEZA yells]
What? It's that guy?!
But how? He was shish-kabob!
These Earth-scum tricksters!
They're just like weeds!
You have to get 'em by the root!
Argh, you wouldn't dare!
Destructo Disk!
[GOKU thinking]
Krillin's back!
And he's just as strong
as ever! But how?
[KRILLIN] Hey, Frieza!
What? Rrrrgh!
I dare ya! Try it one more time!
Here! Here's your target, baby!
Damn you! Fool!
You're a dead man!
[KRILLIN] I've got to keep
him away from Gohan
for a little while.
And, somehow, I've got to
stay alive while doing it.
[KRILLIN] C'mon, you can
do it! Stay focused!
Don't lose your cool!
Don't even look back!
[FRIEZA] You're a dead man!
Oh, man!
[KRILLIN] I shouldn't
have looked!
Huh?
[KRILLIN] This might
buy me a little time...
[KRILLIN screams]
What fun! I love Cat and Mouse!
This one's even small
enough to eat, yum!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN screams]
[various screaming and shouting]
Man!
Fool! You can't hide!
[FRIEZA] Ha, ha, ha! That should
do it! I'll smoke him out!
[KRILLIN coughs]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Hello, there. You've
been quite the trouble-maker,
haven't you?
Well I do have a sense of humor,
and it was all in good fun
except for one minor detail.
You cut off my tail and now
I'm going to eat you for dinner!
This guy's nuts! Well...
Here goes nothing.
Haaah!
Ah, just what I needed! A little
fishing to relax my nerves!
I left my fishing rod at home.
So I guess I'll have
to blast him out.
[FRIEZA] Well, here it goes!
Mmm?
[FRIEZA] Enough of this!
I'm wasting my time!
[FRIEZA] There are much
bigger fish in the sea!
Hyaah!
Solar Flare!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA groans]
You'll pay!
[DENDE] Gohan, it's me, Dende.
Stay calm! You're gonna be fine!
Dende...
Those damn Earthlings!
They're going to pay for this!
Comin' through!
Look out, everyone!
Huh...?
[VEGETA gasps]
So that's how they did it!
Hey, man, are you deaf
or something? Huh? Huh?
Hey, right on!
Mission accomplished!
You mind telling me why in
the heck you fools decided
to keep that kid's
power a secret from me?!
What d'you mean? We didn't
know he could heal people!
If we had known that,
don't you think we would have
had him heal Goku?!
[GOHAN laughs]
[DENDE] Alright, Gohan!
[DENDE giggles]
Gosh, Dende, you're super!
This is so cool! I feel great!
[DENDE] No problem!
[FRIEZA] Huhhh...?
Oh, great! Look who's back?
What? Him too?!
[GOHAN growls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
The kid's a true
Saiyan, all right.
His power level increases
after every battle.
His rage is red hot.
[GOHAN growls]
Right!
Oh, ho, ho, lookit him,
he's flustered.
I think we might just actually
have a chance to beat him
if we attack together!
What's wrong? I clobber
them and then...
Maybe they did wish
for immortality!
Let's hit 'im, boys!
[shouting]
[FRIEZA yells]
Is that the best you can do?
You're pathetic!
Really. Is that it?
I think you better come up with
a new game plan, pretty soon.
Ah... What now?
I don't know!
[GOHAN growls]
There's nothing to do! He's
much stronger! But who cares?!
Sometimes you've got
to attack head on!
Hey! Wait!
[VEGETA] No, don't!
It's suicide!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Hmm?
Huh?!
It's Piccolo!
Am I dreaming?
Is it really you?
Good to see you, Gohan.
[GOHAN laughs]
So it worked! The Dragon came
through for us after all!
This is incredible!
So that's him? Frieza?
[GOHAN] Yeah,
that's him alright.
I see. King Kai thinks he's
unbeatable. We'll find out.
You're right. We will.
But who are you?
Just another weak Namekian?
Wait, I recognize you.
You're the one we destroyed
so easily on Earth.
I can't believe these
fools wasted their wishes
bringing you back to life.
Do me a favor. Just keep
your big mouth shut.
Then, after we beat Frieza,
it'll be you and
me, head to head.
Yeah, like that's
actually going to happen.
[VEGETA laughs]
I guess some people just aren't
satisfied with dying only once,
are they?
[KRILLIN] Man, I hope Piccolo
knows what he's doing...
I can tell that he's a
lot stronger than before,
but I'm not sure if he really
knows what he's up against here.
I suggest you go about
your business, Namekian.
As of yet, I haven't decided
to kill you, but I'm real close.
Now go before it's too late.
Please, it would ease my
conscience knowing
that I spared one of you.
[GOKU thinking] Someone
else has arrived, but who?
Is it... Piccolo?
No, it can't be!
Whoever it is is much
stronger than Piccolo.
Gohan seems to be
completely fine now.
That's a mystery in itself...
What in the world is
going on out there?
None of it makes any sense!
Enough! Come on, I'd like to
do this while I'm still young!
Alright, guys! Just stay out
of this if you don't mind!
Huh?!
They didn't say that
Piccolo was a Namek!
Oh, wow, this is incredible!
[PICCOLO] I think
it would be best
if you took cover
somewhere, Dende.
What...?
Do it!
O-oh! U-uh right!
Whoa! How does he know who I am?
[GOHAN] Man, guys, I don't
like this. Piccolo!
No way! I know he's strong
but I'm just not sure he can
really do it all by himself!
Look at him. He's
determined to win or die!
This'll be a great show! I guess
I'll just kick back and watch!
[GOKU thinking] Uh-oh...
Everybody's just standing
still out there!
I don't like it!
Something major is
about to go down!
[NARRATOR] With the
help of the Dragon,
Piccolo has crossed
over dimensions
and through time and space to
arrive at the battlefield.
But is the mighty Namek biting
off more than he can chew?
Perhaps his
challenge will buy Goku
the precious time that he
needs to regain his strength.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z!