[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Bulma, Krillin, and Gohan
reached Piccolo's homeworld
of Namek in their quest
for the Dragon Balls.
Little did they know,
the forces of evil
were also converging on
this once peaceful planet.
The worst among them...
The sinister Lord Frieza.
Who, with his merciless
band of henchmen,
had already
managed to sweep
four of the seven Dragon
Balls into his clutches...
Lord Frieza, we've
detected a group of Nameks,
not far in
that direction.
Well, that's good news.
And with any luck,
they'll have the fifth Dragon
Ball in their possession.
[NARRATOR] As these villains
scoured the planet,
it was all our three
young heroes could do
to stay out
of harm's way.
[KRILLIN] They'll catch us if we
don't find a place to hide!
[BULMA panting]
I found a cave. It should
be a great spot to lie low.
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
trouble has come
looking for them!
And they're about
to come face-to-face
with the greatest evil they
have ever known... Today!
On Dragon Ball Z!
[GOHAN] Krillin, are
you sensing that?
That energy...
Yeah, it feels pretty strong,
and it's still rising!
Whoever that is, it's--
Trouble! Everyone!
Into the cave!
What's going on?
Bulma, get in here!
[BULMA] I'm coming!
I'm coming!
[BULMA] Now are you gonna tell
me what's going on or not?
I don't see anything!
[KRILLIN] Shh! Quiet.
They're coming right for us.
So what do you think?
Do you think they spotted us?
I don't know...
[KRILLIN] There!
[BULMA squealing]
[squealing continues]
It looks like
they're gone.
That was close. But I don't
think they noticed us.
They didn't even slow
down at all. I don't know.
They must be heading
after something else.
Huh?
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[GOHAN panting]
What is it, you guys?
What's the matter?
[KRILLIN] Bulma, you'd better
check the Dragon Radar...
'Kay. But why?
When... When we
checked it before,
those four Dragon
Balls we saw,
all gathered in the same
place... Look again.
See if they're
still there.
Yeah, sure.
I got it.
[BULMA] They're... They're
moving. All four of them!
Whoever those
guys are,
they have the Dragon
Balls with them!
[KRILLIN] I was
afraid of that...
This is bad.
Real bad.
Gohan!
[KRILLIN] Gohan!
[GOHAN] Sorry.
[KRILLIN] Believe me,
I understand.
So you saw that guy
flying near the front?
Yeah... Yeah, I
saw him all right.
H-He was
like, pure evil.
And his power level's the
highest I've ever sensed.
Me too. And I've
got a bad feeling
this is the same guy
those kids told us about.
I don't know. It might not
be Frieza, but either way
our situation has just
gotten a whole lot worse.
Why? I mean, he can't be
stronger than Vegeta, can he?
I'd say he is and not just
a little bit, either.
I mean a lot.
Not to mention all those
other guys he had with him.
And we've gotta
figure out a way
to get the Dragon
Balls from them!
How're we
gonna do that?
Quick, quick, look!
They're heading directly
for another Dragon Ball.
It's like they know
just where it is!
[KRILLIN] Oh, that's just great!
So they have radar, too.
Which way?
[BULMA] Over there.
The Dragon Radar
says it's about
ten miles that way.
Hey, Krillin, while
we were walking,
didn't you sense a
group of Namekians
coming from
that direction?
Right. Well,
I guess we better go
find out what's up.
I'm going with you!
What?! Are you
guys nuts?
What about me?! You can't just
leave me here all by myself!
[KRILLIN] All right. You can
come chase the bad guys
with us if
you really want.
Well, I suppose I
could come along.
But, then again, it might
be best for one of us
to stay and hold down the
fort, don't you think?
Good idea, Bulma.
Now, don't do
anything stupid!
Remember, Gohan, keep your
power level pushed down
so they don't spot us
coming. Think you got it?
Yeah.
Be safe, you guys. I can't
make it home without you.
Which reminds me, I'd
better call Master Roshi
and let him know
what's going on!
[RADIO] In other news,
rebuilding of
East City continues,
as its citizens work
to reclaim their city
after the devastation
of the recent alien invasion.
--[ROSHI caterwauling]
--The mayor has issued
a statement, saying that
barring further alien attacks,
the reconstruction
of East City should be
completed by year's end...
[phone ringing]
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Keep your pants on.
Roshi here.
Oh, Bulma!
So, how are things
going up there on Namek?
What? WHAT?! Oh no...
Say, Doc, so
when do you think
I'll be able to start
working out again?
Goku, what is
wrong with you?
I'm afraid you're going
to have to rest up
for at least a
little while yet.
Aw, Come on, Doc!
I'm getting weaker
by the minute just
sitting here in bed!
Knock, knock!
Hello in there!
Roshi!
Hello, everyone!
Good to see you.
Um, is ChiChi around
here anywhere?
Why, yes, as a matter of
fact, she is around here.
Oops! I-I mean, hi!
Don't get any ideas.
I'll be right back.
Yeesh...
Touchy thing!
Goku, big news
from Namek.
I just got a hold of
Bulma a little while ago.
[NURSE screaming]
What are you doing?!
Oh, sorry, I, uh, talk with
my hands when I'm excited.
So, then, how are
they? Is Gohan okay?
Well, you know,
they all arrived
on the planet
safely. But...
I'm afraid the good
news ends there...
See, it's Vegeta...
Evidently, he's on Namek, too,
completely healed and
stronger than ever.
No way!
Vegeta?!
And believe it or not,
it gets worse.
It looks like there's
someone else there.
An evil being,
stronger than Vegeta!
On top of that, Bulma
said their spaceship's
been damaged
in an attack.
She doesn't think
she can fix it.
So, they're stuck there?
[ROSHI] It seems they need help
in more ways than one right now.
I'm just worried about
this stronger force.
Yeah, me too.
I mean, someone even more
powerful than Vegeta?
Who could it be?
Hey, what's going on?
Actually, I don't
really wanna know.
But I got somethin' here
that should cheer you up.
It took forever, so I
hope you're grateful.
A gift from Korin.
One bag of
fresh-picked Senzu beans.
Should have you up
and runnin' in no time.
Oh, yeah! Yajirobe!
Perfect timing!
You have no idea how
much I need those!
Hold on. You're not giving any
strange foods to my patient!
Sorry, Doc.
[BOTH whimpering]
[chuckling]
This is great!
I've been waiting forever to
get out of these dinky pajamas.
And back into the uniform
King Kai gave me!
Yeah... Finally!
There! Now no time
to waste. Off to Planet Namek!
Thanks for the
Senzu Beans.
From the sound of things,
I think I'll need 'em.
But, Goku! How in the world are
you planning to get to Namek?
Oh, well, when Bulma's dad came
to visit not too long ago,
I asked him if he could build
another spaceship for me.
I thought it'd be
good to have one,
in case something
like this came up.
Oh, so then he figured out how
to build a ship like Kami's?
No. He
couldn't do that.
He said Kami's ship was made
with a bunch of materials
that are probably
only found on Namek.
What? So...
So, I remembered
the ship I came in here
as a baby was
never destroyed.
At worst, it should
just be a little rusty
from sitting out
there all these years.
Dr. Brief said he'd find
it for me and fix it up!
And seeing as how he's as good
with technology as Bulma,
I'll bet it's
ready to go!
Heh, heh!
Good thinkin'!
Do me a favor, and tell
ChiChi not to worry about me.
Tell her I'm just going
to make sure Gohan
and the others
are all right.
They're gonna need some help
if that mystery person's
power level is anywhere near
as high as you say it is.
Tell her I'll be back
as soon as I can!
Flying Nimbus!
Well, wish me luck.
[DOCTOR stuttering]
[BOTH squealing]
[GOKU] See ya', guys!
[CHICHI humming]
What? That's Goku!
Just what in the world?!
Where do you think
you're going?!
You didn't even pack
clean underwear!
You know what he
is, don'tcha?
[ROSHI]
Hm? What's that?
[YAJIROBE]
Crazy, that's what!
He's not even out
of bed five minutes,
and he's already rushin'
off to another battle!
Goku's always loved
a good challenge.
And he's sworn to protect those
who can't protect themselves.
On top of that,
he's a Saiyan,
so the thirst for battle
is in his blood.
So, he's a Saiyan. Well,
that definitely explains it.
He's not just crazy.
He's crazy and he's
from another planet!
[thinking] I can't believe
there's another fighter
out there that's even
stronger than Vegeta!
I just hope Gohan and Krillin
can hold things together
'til I get to Namek!
Gohan, you're putting
out too much energy!
Keep it as
low as you can!
Right, got it.
[MRS. BRIEF singing happily]
Oh, Goku!
[giggles]
Sorry to
just drop in.
Don't mention it!
Are you feeling better?
Yeah. Strong as an ox.
So, does your husband have that
spaceship ready for me yet?
Oh, goodness, no.
Not even close.
But he's still
working on it.
Not even close?!
I mean, really?
[MRS. BRIEF] Tell you what.
Why don't we go check on him?
[GOKU] Oh, thanks.
[MRS. BRIEF] And
how's that adorable
little boy of yours doing?
I'm just dying to
finally meet him.
I bet he's getting to be
quite the looker. Handsome!
Just like his big,
strong father.
He's doing okay.
And, he's turning out to
be a heck of a fighter!
A chip off the old
block, huh?
And how is ChiChi?
I haven't seen her since
I don't know when.
Shame on you, Goku!
You really need to come
visit more often! You know?
Yeah, well
I've been busy.
[MRS. BRIEF] Oh, sweetums!
Darling! Goku's here to see you!
Wow... I don't believe it.
So this is my ship, huh?
I didn't think it
would be so big!
[MRS. BRIEF] Honey!
[DR. BRIEF] Oh, Goku! You're
looking much better!
[GOKU] I'm all healed
and ready to go.
I was actually
wondering
if you were done with
my spaceship yet.
Still a few bugs to
work out. Come on in.
I'll be right back with
some refreshments, 'kay?
Oh, sure. Thank you!
Oh, wow!
It's huge!
I can't believe you did
all this! It's incredible!
Not really. Just hard work
and a bit of elbow grease.
It looks like it's got
everything I need.
Glad you like it.
But, I won't lie to you...
It wasn't an easy task.
Your old ship was
practically demolished!
I was able to salvage the
engine and a few key parts,
but otherwise I had to
build this from scratch!
But I thought my ship
would've been okay!
That's weird.
I must've smashed it
when I was a baby
or something.
Who knows? Anyway, I
installed everything
you asked for.
Even the training stuff.
Really? Wait, even the
artificial gravity machine?
Ha! She's right
over here.
[GOKU] Perfect!
So, how does it work?
Here's the knob
that controls
how much gravity
you're training under.
You can set it to go anywhere
from double to 100 times
the Earth's
natural gravity.
Be careful you don't end
up like a pancake, though.
Because that's exactly
what'll happen to you
if you set the machine
too high too soon.
This isn't a toy. So please,
use extreme caution.
Don't worry, I will.
But I'm gonna have to
do some heavy training
before I
get to Namek.
So, how much longer until
she's ready to fly?
She's ready now! Anywhere in
the universe you want to go.
Ah! What?
[DR. BRIEF] And there's a full
kitchen down this way.
And to get to the bathroom,
you follow the green arrows.
[GOKU] Wait a second! I thought
you said it wasn't finished yet!
And that's the truth. It isn't
finished. Far from it.
I haven't installed
the cappuccino machine yet.
What?! Are you kidding? I
don't care about cappuccino!
Well, you say that now,
but wait until you wake up
and you want a nice
warm breakfast beverage
to start your
day off right.
[GOKU whining]
But, there's no time!
I'm in a big hurry!
I've got to get to the
others right away! Really!
[DR. BRIEF] Just another day
or two. What's the rush?
[GOKU] We got a
call from Bulma
saying they need
my help on Namek!
[DR. BRIEF] Hmm...
C'mon! Just teach me how to
fly this thing so I can go!
Are you positive you're okay
without the cappuccino machine?
Uh-huh!
Well, all the data's
been entered already.
All you have to do
is push the button,
and you're
off to Namek.
You should arrive there in
under six days, give or take.
Six days! Great!
That means I can definitely get
there in time to help them out!
[MRS. BRIEF singing]
Hey! I heard
Goku was here!
Oh, sure! He's
out checking on
the spaceship if
you wanna see him.
[engines igniting]
[OOLONG] You mean
that spaceship?
[OOLONG and PUAR screaming]
[MRS. BRIEFS] Ohh!
[SCRATCH yowling]
Let's see... I think he
said it was this button.
Uhh...
[GOKU squeals]
[DR. BRIEF] Well, what do
you know? It actually works.
Sometimes I amaze
even myself.
Dr. Brief!
Where's Goku?
On his way to
Planet Namek.
[DR. BRIEF] Probably wishing
he had cappuccino already.
We're close. They
must be right up there
over that ridge, Gohan.
We should walk from here.
Okay!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, feel that?
It's really strong now.
C'mon, we'll get a
better look from up there.
[GOHAN] Right.
Keep really low
to the ground.
[GOHAN] Hmm.
Just our luck, we're
right in front of 'em!
Let's go around.
Right!
[GOHAN] Hey!
That looks just like
the spaceship
we came here in.
[KRILLIN] That's weird.
I thought they had a radar,
but it looks like
they're still searching...
And there's that guy in
the hover vehicle again.
He's definitely
the one in charge.
His power
level's massive!
Yeah, you're
not kidding.
Uh? Ahh!
Check it out! Take a
look at what those guys
have tucked under their arms!
It's the Dragon Balls!
I can't believe
the size of them.
Huh?
[FRIEZA]
What's wrong, Dodoria?
Does your scouter
indicate something?
I don't know. For a second,
I thought I detected
a very weak power level.
And then it just disappeared.
It's probably just a bird,
or a small rodent.
Nothing that should
cause us any alarm.
[GOHAN and KRILLIN whimpering]
[KRILLIN] We gotta be careful.
Cuz, if they spot us,
we're as good as dead!
[HENCHMAN] Lord Frieza,
we only found five of them.
We're bringing
them out now.
It looks like the others
ran off before we got here.
Let's get moving!
Believe me, you don't want to
make me come in after you!
Huh...?
They look just
like Piccolo!
Guess we found
the Nameks...
[FRIEZA chuckles]
It sure is dark out here.
Pretty lonely, too.
[GOKU] But I've got a
lot of work to do
if I wanna get my power level
up as high as Vegeta's.
I might as well go ahead
and start training now.
It's not like I have anything
better to do in this place.
Now, let's see...
I trained at 10 times gravity
on King Kai's planet.
So I should probably
start higher than that.
[GOKU] 'Kay... Gravitational
level set to...
Twenty.
[GOKU grunting]
Whoa!
[grunting continues]
Shoulda' tried 11.
[NARRATOR] Goku speeds
toward the Planet Namek
in an effort to
join his friends.
But with only six days
in which to train,
can he possibly prepare himself
for the terrible new foe
he will face
once he arrives?
The shadow of
Frieza looms large...
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!