[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Piccolo and Nail
fused into one being.
And while Goku was
still trying to heal,
the battle between
Frieza and the warriors
from the planet Earth began.
Fool!
[NARRATOR] Luckily, Vegeta
became their ally once again,
and was taking most of the
heat from the evil super-power.
[NARRATOR] With Vegeta's
increased strength,
it seemed like an even match
between the two warriors.
[NARRATOR] But Vegeta knew
that Frieza was holding back
and he began to talk
Frieza into transforming
and revealing his true power!
[NARRATOR] But look out!
Perhaps pushing for
the transformation
wasn't the wisest
decision after all.
What danger awaits Krillin,
Gohan, and Vegeta now?
Find out today!
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN shout]
[FRIEZA] Ahh...
[BOTH whimper]
[FRIEZA giggles]
So? Who do you think
you're fooling?
You grew two inches and
got rid of your armor!
You call that a transformation?
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA] Oh, Vegeta, it pains me
to see you behaving this way.
What a waste. I had
favored you so much.
Why couldn't you just
have continued to obey me?
Obey? I only pretended
to obey you, you idion!
I've been waiting patiently
for any chance I could get to
destroy you once and for all!
Yes, you're just like
you're father, aren't you?
The good king.
[FRIEZA] You probably don't
remember your father very well,
do you Vegeta?
[KING VEGETA] What? The planet
Tazbah hasn't been occupied yet?
No, Sire! The resistance
there is much stronger
than we ever expected.
We're now estimating
three more days.
Three days?!
[SOLDIER] Yes, Sire.
[KING VEGETA] Have you forgotten
that we promised to
deliver that planet
to Lord Frieza by tomorrow?!
No, of course not, Sire. I know!
But the full moon there
is three days away...
[KING VEGETA] Get lost!
[SOLDIER] Sire?
What's wrong? You heard me!
[SOLDIER screams]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[KING VEGETA] Hm?
[FRIEZA] You're such
a brute, Vegeta.
Those two days
didn't matter to me.
Oh, well! Too late.
You don't mind if
I sit down, do you?
Ah, that's better. Very comfy.
Now, are we still in
agreement about your son?
Yes, we are. You can have him.
[KING VEGETA growls]
Splendid!
You can bring him when
you come to inform me
about the progress on Tazbah.
Hmph.
You should try to be a little
more lenient on your subjects.
[FRIEZA laughs]
Please, Sire. We can't
hand over the Prince to him!
I'd rather die than do that!
Me too. But for now
we'll do as he says...
[ELITE SAIYAN] Please, Sire.
I don't have a choice, Zorn!
We have to strike when
the time is right!
If we act too hastily, they'll
be nothing left worth defending.
Yes, my King.
[KING VEGETA] Don't worry,
we'll have our day.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA] Oh, yes,
he had his day alright.
Just like you're
having yours now.
Do you remember?
What are you saying?!
You were there, safely tucked
away in the bowels of my ship
while your father was
making his ill-fated plans.
[KING VEGETA] Remember now,
the Prince is on
board Frieza's ship,
so we want to try
and keep it intact.
[KING VEGETA] You are the
greatest fighters on our planet.
You are the elite!
Together you will fight and
together you will conquer!
[ZARBON] Lord Frieza!
King Vegeta has arrived escorted
by a squadron of his men.
He's requested an
audience with you.
Lord Frieza?
[FRIEZA] Zarbon, you would be
well-advised not to rush me.
Yes...
Now open the doors.
[ZARBON] As you wish, my lord.
Some of you, go! Take that way!
[CAPTAIN] There they are!
[KING VEGETA shouts]
[screams]
[grunting]
[KING VEGETA] Raaagh!
[HENCHMEN scream]
[distant rumbling]
[FRIEZA] Why, those
nasty monkeys!
Zarbon! Go ahead
and open my door.
Vegeta wanted an
audience with me
and that's what
he's going to get.
Right!
[FRIEZA] This is no way for
guests on my ship to behave!
[KING VEGETA] Frieza!
We have some business!
[KING VEGETA] It's over, Frieza!
We've come to put an end
to your reign of terror!
"We"? You and who else, Vegeta?
Your army is so petrified
that they're actually
turning blue in the face!
Hmm?
[KING VEGETA growls]
Fools!
The King! No!
Hm?
[FRIEZA] My, my, what a pity.
[ELITE SAIYANS gasp]
[FRIEZA] Don't be so glum guys.
You haven't lost
your king for good.
Wherever he is,
you're about to join him!
[ELITE SAIYANS growl]
[FRIEZA growls]
[ELITE SAIYANS scream]
I say we torch the
whole barrel of monkeys!
How 'bout it, Zarbon?
Is it necessary now that
Vegeta's out of the way?
Yes, because when one revolts,
the others are sure to follow!
You know, monkey see, monkey do!
[ZARBON gasps]
[ZARBON] Well...
I suppose you know best.
[FRIEZA] Just look at
all those lost sheep
waiting for the good
news from their king!
[FRIEZA cackles]
What? No!
[BARDOCK screams]
[ELITE SAIYANS scream]
[FRIEZA cackles]
Oh, my! This is... stupendous!
Wow! What a great show!
Unbelievable! Just look at that!
[FRIEZA cackles]
[FRIEZA] I really wanted you
to enjoy the fireworks, Vegeta.
They were to...
die for!
[VEGETA] How absurd! You
were afraid of the Saiyans
so you destroyed
their entire race
along with their whole planet.
And yet, you left
the strongest one alive.
You fool! This is one mistake
you're going pay dearly for!
[FRIEZA] Why you insolent tree
monkey! I've had enough of this!
You're the one who's
going to pay!
Talk! All you are
is a bunch of talk!
Allow me to show you something
that not even your father
saw in his lifetime!
What now?
[FRIEZA growls]
[shouting]
[FRIEZA yells]
[BOTH whimper]
[BULMA grunts]
Oh, man! I can't even go on.
No reason to live anymore,
except to get even
with those jerks!
[distant rumbling]
Hm?
[BULMA gasps]
[distant rumbling continues]
What the heck? What is it?
Hmm?!
[BULMA screams]
[roaring]
Why me?! Why me?!
[BULMA] A cave!
Oh, my gosh!
[roaring]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] Oh, no! I'm lunch meat!
[BULMA] Hm?
Hey, what's the deal?
What in the world
are they scared of?
[FRIEZA screams]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN whimper]
[screaming continues]
Oh, crap!
[FRIEZA screaming]
[distorted screaming]
[roaring]
[VEGETA gasps]
[whimpering]
[roaring]
Unbelievable! Absolute madness!
It was nice knowing
you, Krillin...
Yeah... So long, Gohan...
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Well, this is it! I hope
you're not disappointed.
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU] Uh-oh!
Something's not right.
Holy smoke!
All of a sudden it feels
like there are ten Friezas!
Hang on, Gohan!
[whimpering]
[FRIEZA] My, my, what's the
matter with you little insects?
You seem frightened!
Vegeta, you're speechless.
Don't tell me that you've run
out of bold threats already?
Such paultry playthings.
Not worth transforming for,
but I guess some amusement
is better than none.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOHAN] Wow...
Yeah. It retracts!
You like that, huh?
Why, thank you.
Most opponents never see it
coming! I'm somewhat impressed.
By the way, Vegeta.
Did I happen to mention
that my fighting power in
this form is over a million?
What? No way!
One million?
[VEGETA] I-I don't believe it!
That's impossible, even for him!
So, some non-believers, huh?
Well, allow me to demonstrate.
[grunting]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[PICCOLO] What's going on?!
No way! It's Frieza! How could
he have so much power? How?!
[GOHAN] Krillin! Hey, Krillin!
Where are you?!
[KRILLIN] Gohan!
Huh? You okay?
[KRILLIN grunts]
Nah! I'm fine! It's just
a scratch, no problem!
Now what's wrong? Please!
I can't take the long faces.
Cheer up! It's a beautiful day
to die! Don't you agree, Vegeta?
I mean really, what else
could you ask for?
The sun is shining!
The sea is a sparkly blue!
The mountains can be
seen in the background!
It's positively perfect!
Now all we have to do is decide
which one of you
gets to die first.
[DENDE] Krillin, I'm scared...
[FRIEZA] Now, let's see...
Hmmm...
[GOHAN gasps]
[DENDE whimpers]
[DENDE] Krillin...
[FRIEZA shouts]
Huh?!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[DENDE] Nooo!
Krillin! No!
My god!
[KRILLIN whimpers softly]
[DENDE whimpers]
[NARRATOR] Darkness
has descended
and the valiant Krillin
has met his end.
Can the monstrous
Frieza be stopped
before any more blood is shed?
No! How could you?!
[NARRATOR] On the
next Dragon Ball Z.