[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
ready to do their
part to stop Majin Buu,
Trunks and Goten charged up
their Super Saiyan powers
for their first lesson
in the fusion technique.
[GOKU] Good, now raise
it to your maximums.
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere, the wizard
Babidi managed to uncover
some valuable information,
and paused his
spree of destruction
just long enough to make a
very important announcement.
[BABIDI using ESP] Attention,
Earthlings! Attention!
So sorry to
bother you once again.
Trunks, I am
very eager to meet you.
And I suppose that if I
can't get you to come to me,
then I'll just have
to come to where you live.
[BABIDI laughs]
[BABIDI] It's a place
called Capsule Corporation
and it's located in West City.
I hope that you're there
to greet me when I arrive,
because if you're not,
then your family and friends
will have to pay the price.
Goku, if we let Majin Buu get
to West City and destroy it
then he'll destroy
the Dragon Radar!
[NARRATOR]
In light of this new crisis,
Goku sent Trunks on a mission
to find the Dragon Radar.
Meanwhile, he would
try to slow down
Babidi and Buu by himself!
[GOKU] Yeah, but you let me
worry about them.
I'll be all right.
Hi.
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu was more
than pleased by Goku's arrival,
eager to face a new and
interesting challenge.
And that's exactly what Goku
was prepared to give him!
[NARRATOR] Unless Goku can
buy Trunks enough time
to retrieve the Dragon Radar,
all hope of repairing
Majin Buu's damage
to the Earth will be lost!
But in order to keep this
bizarre monster occupied,
Goku may need to use to some
unconventional tactics!
[GOKU]
I'm guessing an ascended Saiyan
isn't much of a
challenge for you.
So how about I take
it up to the next level?
As interested as I am
to see this trick of yours,
time is short.
The good people of
West City are expecting us.
Maybe next time.
Majin Buu! Hurry up and
do something nasty to him.
We have an appointment to keep.
[BUU]
Whoa-ho-ho, yeah!
Whoo, whoo-whoo! Whee! Whoo!
[laughs]
[thinking]
From the way he acts,
you'd never guess he could
really be that strong.
Then again, Vegeta probably
thought the same thing.
[thinking]
I'll have to be careful.
I only have to
distract him long enough
for Trunks to
find the Dragon Radar.
Don't worry.
It won't be long. I'm sure
Trunks has made it home by now.
No, no he hasn't.
[thinking] What?! Why is
Trunks just sitting still?
We don't have time for him to
stop and check out the scenery!
He better hurry.
I don't want to go beyond the
second level if I don't have to.
I don't know, that power
I'm sensing... it's so huge.
What if it's
really that monster?
Goten's dad will need my help!
Oh, what am
I s'posed to do?!
I wish he'd give
me a sign or something!
[GOKU growls]
What are you doing?!
[grunts]
Stop goofing off
and get the radar!
Ahh, yeah!
What? "Radar"?
Did I just miss something here?
Who in the world
are you talking to?
And what's this
"radar" nonsense?
Don't worry,
it's not your problem.
I guess that settled that,
Goten's dad has
it under control.
But still, he didn't
have to yell at me.
I was only tryin' to help.
[BABIDI giggles]
Perhaps you're so terrified that
you've begun to hallucinate,
is that it?
Perhaps.
[thinking] I still need to
buy some more time.
Guess I'm gonna have to give
these guys a demonstration.
Why you go down? You no play?
[GOKU]
We'll get to that.
First, I thought
I'd take a minute
to teach you a thing
or two about Super Saiyans
starting with the basics.
Super Saiya-jin?
Don't bother with it, I never
asked you to explain anything.
You're going
to love this, trust me.
What you're seeing
now is my normal state.
This is a Super Saiyan.
And this... this is what
is known as a Super Saiyan
that has ascended
past a Super Saiyan.
Or, you could just
call this a Super Saiyan 2.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Ho-hum. What a
useless transformation.
You've changed
your hair, so what?
[GOKU chuckles]
Just wait.
Has he really found a way to
surpass an ascended Saiyan?
Is that possible?
He must be bluffing,
I mean, what would that
make him, double ascended?
And this...
What's he doing?
...is to go even further beyond!
[yells]
[gasping]
[GOKU yells]
No, stop it, Goku!
If you do this now,
it's going to drain away all
the time you have left on Earth!
And I'd say you need every
second of it as it is!
[GOKU yells]
[BUU]
Oohhh...
[gasps]
[GOKU yells]
It's... unreal. How is he
generating that much power?!
Do it, Dad!
It's... too much!
[gasps]
What's going on?
Goten's dad is putting out
even more energy than before!
I should go. I don't want
to get yelled at again!
[GOKU yells]
[screaming]
[yells]
[whimpers]
[GOKU yells]
Stop it! Stop it now, Goku!
[PEOPLE gasping, screaming]
[gasping]
With terror in the streets--
[GOKU yells]
It feels like the
whole world is shaking apart.
What is Goku doing?
If he doesn't stop this
everything is
going to be destroyed!
[whimpers]
Please, somebody, make it stop!
[yells]
[APE GOKU roars]
[GOKU yells]
[screams]
[BUU]
Oooh! Ooh-oooh-oooooh!
[gasps]
[yells]
[gasping]
I'm sorry that took so
much longer than the others.
But I haven't had much
occasion to practice this one.
This is what I
call a "Super Saiyan 3."
[whimpers]
[BUU]
Ooooh!
There's a Super Saiyan 3 now?
Do you feel that energy?
If I didn't know better,
I'd say that was my dad!
But that's... crazy.
It IS Goku!
I have no idea how,
but it's definitely your father.
I'm certain.
That... That can't be Goku!
Saiyan powers are not strong
enough to be felt this far away.
Well, it is. And I don't
think that's a good thing.
[growls]
Buu not scared.
Big hair make you big funny.
Yes, I'm inclined to agree.
This "Super Three" whatever you
said, it's ridiculous.
Majin Buu, I think our friend's
in need of a haircut.
I'm ready,
show me what you've got.
[laughs]
[BABIDI]
We will! You and everyone else!
The whole world will be watching
when Buu pounds
you into oblivion!
Pow! Pow-Pow!
[thinking] Trunks,
you better move it fast.
[TRUNKS]
Yeah, I made it!
Bulma, Trunks has just landed!
All right!
It'll just take him a second
to get the radar from my dad.
Then we're home free!
[TRUNKS]
Grandpa!
[DR. BRIEF]
Well...
How's my grandson today?
[MRS. BRIEF]
Oh, hi, Trunks.
What great timing,
I just made some tea.
No, we've gotta hurry!
Okay then.
I have some fresh vanilla
ice cream in the freezer.
Do you want a sundae?
There's not time for ice cream!
Well, let's see...
Would you rather have a nice
big sandwich, some roast beef?
I just sliced it myself.
You're not listening to me,
Grandpa, where do we
keep the Dragon Radar?
Dragon Radar?
[TRUNKS]
Mm-hmm! Mm-hmm!
Ah... Well, the last time
I saw it, it was umm...
Hurry up! We don't have time!
[BABIDI growls]
Do it! Take him down!
Buu!
[gasps]
[screams]
[BUU grunts]
Oh no!
[BUU yells]
[grunts]
[BUU whimpers]
[GOKU yells]
[BUU grunts]
[gasps]
[BUU grunting]
Fight back! Do something!
[grunting continues]
[KRILLIN]
Oh yeah!
I don't see why Goku didn't
do this in the first place!
I knew it! No one in the
world can beat my dad!
Perhaps.
It's true that
Goku has proven
to be stronger
than any of us imagined.
But the chances he'll be
able to stop Majin Buu
by himself are still slim.
Well, if Goku can't do it,
is there anyone who can?
I hope.
Hey, somebody's
fighting with Majin Buu!
Who is it?
I don't know,
but he's my new best friend!
You take that
fat tub of lard down!
[BUU grunting]
What are you doing?! Buu!
[GOKU yells]
[BUU yelps]
[yelling]
[BUU grunting]
[gasps]
[BUU]
Buuuuu!
[screaming]
[BABIDI]
No! What have you done?!
[MAN D] Did he actually win?
Is that thing dead?
[gasping]
[giggles]
[BABIDI] Ha, ha! Welcome back,
Buu! I thought we'd lost you!
[thinking]
He's completely unharmed.
Not so much as a scratch.
[BUU yells]
[thinking] That's one
of Vegeta's attacks!
[growls]
[thinking] Amazing. He can't
have seen it more than once.
But he's already mastered
one of Vegeta's best moves...
[BABIDI] I've had enough of
watching you show off, Buu!
Finish the job!
[GOKU grunts]
[laughs]
Goku, that's enough!
You're using too much power.
Please, please stop it!
While you still have some
time left. The Earth needs you.
You still have to teach
the boys the fusion technique!
[BUU grunts]
[grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[yelling]
Buu have fun playing
with you. You strong.
Thanks, so are you.
Hey, punch him! Don't just
float there like a balloon!
[BUU growls]
[BABIDI] Hurry! Or do you want
me to seal you up again?
Quiet!
What?! You insolent,
portly buffoon!
How dare you
talk to me that way!
I am your master
and I'm ordering you to
grind that man into dust!
[thinking] Trunks hasn't
left Capsule Corp yet.
What's taking so long?
Hey, Trunks, you really
need to get a move on.
What was that?
[TRUNKS] C'mon,
c'mon, stupid radar!
Grandpa, where was the last
place you remember putting it?!
[DR. BRIEF] I'm thinking it
was somewhere in this room.
Ah! I see, so you've
been in contact
with young Trunks all along!
How delightful.
Oh-ho, Buu!
How would you like to
torture our friend here
until he tells us where
that little brat is hiding?!
[giggles]
[thinking] Looks like I still
have to stall for more time.
[BUU]
Ohh... Oh?
[BUU grunts]
[BUU grunting]
That's it, show that
fat blob who's boss!
[GOTEN]
Get him, Dad.
[grunts]
[NARRATOR] Once again,
Goku has defied the impossible
by transforming himself
into a Super Saiyan 3!
[BUU screams]
[NARRATOR] But how long can
these awesome new powers
keep Majin Buu at bay?
[TRUNKS] Where is it?
Where is it? Where is it?
Where is it?!
[NARRATOR] Can Goku win
Trunks the time he needs
to find the Dragon Radar
and escape from West City?
[BUU laughs]
[NARRATOR] Or will he
somehow find a way to do
what can't be done and
finish off Majin Buu by himself?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball Z!