[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z:
[VEGETA] Like what will happen
if I yank this thing down?
Please! Let go! If you
tear those attachments
I won't be me anymore!
That sounds interesting!
Let's give it a try, shall we?
Nooo!!
[chuckles, grunts]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
And so the cord was cut,
linking old Majin Buu to new.
And with another
transformation mounting
it was now or never
for Goku and Vegeta.
They had to get out
of Buu's mutating body
and fast!
[GOKU]
Haa!!
Go!
[GOKU]
Woo-hoo!
[NARRATOR] At last,
the microscopic battle was over.
Goku and Vegeta had
completed their mission
and safely delivered Piccolo,
Gohan, Trunks, and Goten
from their fleshy prison.
But the duo's handiwork
had spurred on
another transformation!
Buu was on the boil and in the
throes of a maddening mutation!
[SUPER BUU screams]
Watch. He's about to change.
Into a better dancer, I hope.
[NARRATOR]
Things were looking grim
as Majin Buu seemed
to be growing
in size and strength!
But when the
dust finally settled,
Buu had assumed a much
smaller form than before.
[GOKU]
Ha! You weren't worried, huh?
You had white knuckles
and you know it!
[NARRATOR]
But was the threat really over?
Kibito Kai doesn't
seem to think so.
What does the appearance
of this new Buu portend?
[MR. SATAN] Look at him now.
He looks like a little kid.
Yeah! It's time for
me to kick some Buu!
No, wait! I wouldn't do that.
Uh...
Yeah! I have a terrible
feeling about this.
It's hard to tell if
he's stronger now or weaker.
Ah, first things first.
Let's find a safe place
to put these guys.
[VEGETA]
Right!
Pod life is no life at all.
[GOKU] No kidding.
I hope they're all right.
[GOKU]
There you go, little man.
[VEGETA]
They did well to stay alive.
That was a feat in of itself.
[GOKU]
Yeah, that's for sure.
[VEGETA thinking]
Trunks...
[GOKU] Why aren't they
snapping out of it?
Hey! Gohan! Wake up, son!
[GOHAN groans]
[gasps]
Vegeta! He's coming to!
He's going to be fine.
[GOKU]
Vegeta?
[OLD KAI]
So this is Buu's original form?
Well! Now I'm confused.
Are you certain?
Yes. I'm dead certain.
[KIBITO KAI]
Many eons ago,
the Supreme Kais were
enjoying a long reign of peace
under Daikaioh,
our benevolent leader.
It was a happy time.
There was the Kai of the North.
And the Supreme Kai of the west.
[WEST SUPREME KAI laughs]
[KIBITO KAI]
And South Kai!
[WEST SUPREME KAI]
Kai, keep up with me.
[SOUTH SUPREME KAI]
Give me that! Hey!
[KIBITO KAI] I was serving
as East Kai back then.
[WEST SUPREME KAI laughs]
[WEST SUPREME KAI]
There, have it!
[SOUTH SUPREME KAI]
Uh... Uh?
[WEST SUPREME KAI]
Happy landing!
[SOUTH SUPREME KAI
whimpers, yells]
[KIBITO KAI] But,
as with most harmonious times,
a period of disharmony
was soon to follow.
[KIBITO KAI] We had no way
to prepare ourselves
for the evil creation
that the wizard Bibidi
was about to unleash
on the Universe.
[screaming]
[BIBIDI cackles]
[BIBIDI]
Yes! Yes!
Yes! Kill them all!
[screaming]
Go, go, go, go! Aaaah!
[KID BUU screams]
[BIBIDI laughs]
Nice coming out party!
Good work, Buu!
[KID BUU screams]
[yells]
[BIBIDI screams]
What are you doing?!
How dare you?! I'm the one who
created you, you stupid idiot!
Hi! I'm your dad.
[grunting]
[WEST SUPREME KAI yells]
[KIBITO KAI] The beautiful
guardian of the West
was the first Kai to
encounter Majin Buu in battle.
[WEST SUPREME KAI grunting]
[KID BUU giggles]
[WEST SUPREME KAI grunts]
[BIBIDI] She's no match
for you, is she?
I'll bet you're bored silly.
[KID BUU shrieks]
[KIBITO KAI] There wasn't even
the slightest bit of mercy
in this strange, new creature.
West Kai knew that their
fight would be to the death.
[WEST SUPREME KAI grunts]
[gasps]
[KIBITO KAI]
And so it was.
[WEST SUPREME KAI gasps,
KID BUU giggles]
[WEST SUPREME KAI screams]
[BIBIDI giggles]
[BIBIDI] Huh? Hey! Where do
you think you're going?!
I'm the one who decides what
we're going to do around here!
[NORTH SUPREME KAI growls]
[KIBITO KAI]
North Kai was the next one
to engage Majin Buu in battle.
Huh?!
[NORTH SUPREME KAI
screams, grunts]
[KIBITO KAI] He, too, met his
end on that dreadful day.
[BIBIDI laughs]
Sir! West Kai and North Kai!
They've both been killed!
[KIBITO KAI]
The South Supreme Kai
was the next one
to join the fray.
[SOUTH SUPREME KAI grunts]
[KID BUU yells]
[KID BUU screams]
[SOUTH SUPREME KAI]
I think this belongs to you.
[KID BUU growls]
[growls, yells]
Huh?!
[SOUTH SUPREME KAI grunts]
[KID BUU squeals]
[SOUTH SUPREME KAI gasps]
[giggles]
[KIBITO KAI]
South Kai was the strongest
and sturdiest among us.
And the first to fall prey
to Buu's absorption technique.
[KID BUU snarls]
[yelling]
[OLD KAI]
Hmm... I think I see now.
That hulking form that
we saw just minutes ago
while Buu was transforming.
That's the form he assumed
when he absorbed South Kai.
Yes...
I, too, would have perished on
that day like all the others.
I didn't stand a chance
against Majin Buu.
I was staring death in the face.
[KID BUU laughs]
[SUPREME KAI growls]
[KID BUU growls]
[SUPREME KAI grunts]
[SUPREME KAI]
Daikaioh!
Yah-haa!
[KID BUU gasps, grunts]
[grunts, screams]
[KIBITO KAI] I had never
seen my benevolent leader
unleash such a furious attack.
Any other adversary
would have been finished.
[gasps]
[growls]
[KIBITO KAI] What I witnessed
after that, I can never forget.
[muffled screaming]
No! I'm the one you wanted!
Let him go!
Whoo! Hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hooo!
Buu! You're fat! Is that
really you under there?
Yup! Me Buu! Me all Buu from
head to toe! Buu very hungry!
Huh? Oh. Well, let's go
find some cake. How's that?
Cake?
Cake! Cake good!
Yes... Ah...
Ahhh! Eh-heh-heh!
Yes, Buu! Cake is the
tastiest food in the universe.
[BUU]
Yipeeee! Cake!
Buu want some now!
[BIBIDI]
Well, okay!
From now on,
I'll feed you cake everyday
if you obey me and
do as I say. How's that?
Buu do!
Buu do! Buu do!
[KIBITO KAI]
In a sense,
Daikaioh not only saved
my life by being absorbed
but the entire universe as well.
Because it was his
innocence and purity
that transformed the
killing machine into the happy,
frolicking Buu!
[OLD KAI] Hmm! Now I finally
get it. They weakened him. Yes!
When he absorbed the Kai's.
Of course! It brought
his power down.
I thought the opposite was true.
[KIBITO KAI] Exactly!
This Buu's even more powerful!
And without the influence of the
Kais' goodness inside of him,
he's evil!
Pure, unrestrained evil!
[GOKU]
Uh-oh! He's on the move.
[shrieks]
[KID BUU shrieks]
[GOKU]
Wow! That's loud!
Will someone shut him up?!
[shrieks]
[GOKU]
What?! Aaaahh!
[VEGETA growls]
Whoa! He's mad!
That blast had enough power
to destroy the entire planet!
Nice shot, man.
What a fool!
Does he want to die, too?!
[GOKU] He was probably planning
on getting blown to bits
and then reforming again!
Hey, Buu!
It's your business if you
want to blow up the planet,
but fight us first,
you little coward!
[hisses]
[chuckles]
Gifted speaker.
[laughs]
[KID BUU growls]
[GOKU] No, no!
That can't be meant for us!
That's way too much energy!
It's enough energy to blow up
the planet ten times!
Vegeta! We can't stop that!
[snarls]
[growls]
Ooh... Whew...
Listen! Bring your earrings to
Goku and Vegeta immediately.
[gasps]
Yes! I see!
You got it!
[KID BUU snarls]
No, Buu! No! Why?
Why are you doing this?!
There'll be nothing! Nothing
left at all! Please, Buu!
[giggles]
[gasps]
[GOKU]
The boys... Piccolo...
Vegeta! We'll grab the boys
and use Instant Transmission!
[VEGETA]
Yes!
[growls]
[GOKU]
Grab hold!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU thinking] It's no good!
I can't concentrate!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Vegeta! Are you on?
G-Go!
[growls]
Her secret was the
teddy-bear underwear!
[laugh]
[KING KAI whimpers]
Yes! Superb! You're still alive!
[GOKU grunts]
Gohan, Goten, and Trunks!
I-I let all of them down!
[MR. SATAN] Uhh! Where am I?
Oh, I died, didn't I?
[growls]
[VEGETA]
And what do we have here?
[growls]
Idiot! How could you?!
You save the Namek boy
and that big oaf
instead of your own sons?!
Have you lost your mind?!
[DENDE]
Vegeta... Sorry...
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] I can't believe that
maniac blew up the Earth...
[NARRATOR] As Goku
wrestles with his decision
and contemplates
the loss of his sons,
and the beautiful Mother Earth,
something begins to
stir amongst the rubble
where the majestic blue
planet once adorned the sky!