[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta summoned all of
his strength into one
ultimate energy blast
and fired it directly at Cell.
[NARRATOR] When the smoke
cleared, Vegeta saw that he had
indeed hit his mark and
disarmed Cell, literally!
[VEGETA laughs]
[NARRATOR] But Vegeta's
celebration was soon cut short,
as Cell demonstrated
his powers of regeneration.
Sprouting a new arm, Cell was
ready for battle once again,
and Vegeta found himself
in a very dangerous situation.
[VEGETA shouting]
[NARRATOR] Despite all of
his new Saiyan powers,
Vegeta could not make a dent
in Cell's monstrous armor.
[NARRATOR] But he
definitely made an impact.
[NARRATOR] With his father
knocked unconscious,
Trunks was ready at last
to unveil his hidden power
and take his turn at Cell.
[TRUNKS grunts]
[NARRATOR] But can
this young warrior
find the strength
to save Vegeta
and battle Cell
all by himself?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball Z!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[CELL] Hmm...
[TRUNKS grunts]
[grunting continues]
What's this?!
[KRILLIN] Trunks...?
Is everything okay...?
Wow! Amazing! His strength
keeps growing and growing!
Trunks wasn't kidding! He really
is stronger than Vegeta now!
Hey, Trunks! Can you hear me?!
What's happening to you?!
Wow! These Saiyans
are incredible!
They just keep on growing!
Every enemy they face takes
them to a new level of power!
Now, it's Trunks' turn.
[KRILLIN gasps]
Hey, Krillin.
I've got a plan... but
I need you to take my father to
Master Roshi's house
so he can recover.
[KRILLIN sighs]
You bet! Man, what a relief!
Trunks, I sure am glad you're
still one of the good guys!
For a minute there I thought you
were gonna pull a Gohan
and go ape!
Don't worry, I'm alright.
[TRUNKS] Just make sure
my father gets this.
It should be enough
to restore his strength
and get him back on his feet.
But, Trunks! What about you?
This is the last Senzu bean.
What if you need it?
I have no use for it, Krillin.
I don't plan on losing.
Well, I really hope you
don't either. Good luck, Trunks!
[thinking] Hmm... I wonder
what Trunks has to offer me?
His power level
has taken a sudden jump.
[thinking] Maybe I will
finally have a challenge.
[CELL] Hmph.
[CELL] Don't you think Vegeta
is right where he belongs?
With his face in the mud?
[CELL chuckles]
It's all over, Cell!
Well, I've heard
that one before.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] You Saiyans
are like cockroaches.
Squash one and another
crawls out from the wall!
[CELL] You know you'll face
the same fate as your father!
[TRUNKS] I don't think so.
Not this time.
[ANDROID 16] Did that boy not
see what happened to Vegeta?
[KRILLIN gulps]
[TRUNKS grunts]
What?!
They disappeared!
Where'd they go?!
I can't see them anywhere!
Huh--?!
[TRUNKS growls]
What was that?!
Wait! I don't see Cell and
Trunks is still standing!
There's no doubt about it.
All that training in the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber
really paid off!
Trunks must be the
strongest fighter
in the universe right now!
[GOKU] Ready to test
your new powers, Gohan?
[GOHAN] Yeah, I'm ready, Dad.
Alright... now catch me...
do whatever it takes.
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN]
There's no use hiding, Dad!
You know I can
sense where you are!
[GOHAN] Raaah!
That's the way! But you'll
have to do better than that!
[GOHAN growls]
Whew! Close one!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOHAN shouting]
[GOKU squeals]
[gasps]
[GOHAN] Gotcha!
[GOKU] Huh?
[GOHAN] How was that?
Not bad.
How about a quick break?
Yeah!
[GOKU laughs]
Well, at least
you missed the fridge.
Oops! Sorry about that.
[GOKU] We'd better
fix this place up
before Mr. Popo sees it.
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Yeah, I guess so!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] Alright!
Trunks did it!
That's great!
I never would have guessed
that he would
be the one to beat Cell!
Wait 'til I tell
the other guys!
Way to go, Trunks!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Krillin, no! Look out!
[KRILLIN] Trun--!
Oh no!
[KRILLIN screams]
[CELL laughs]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[CELL] I know what
you're thinking.
I'm just a nightmare
that won't go away!
Well, wake up, Trunks. I'm real.
[KRILLIN] This guy
is way too creepy!
I don't know what's worse.
Seeing him or hearing him!
[CELL] I said it before,
I'll say it again.
You Saiyans don't know
when to give up.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] You have a
strong fighting spirit.
I will enjoy draining you of it!
[TRUNKS growls]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[TRUNKS yells]
[KRILLIN] Oh man!
Cell will destroy him!
Huh?
[KRILLIN] Whoa... They're
really tearing it up!
[TRUNKS yells]
[CELL grunts]
[TRUNKS shouts]
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS thinking] I must
keep Cell's attention
away from my father!
Well done, Trunks.
I see you've learned
all of Vegeta's moves.
[CELL] Now let me demonstrate
how to do them properly!
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL] Mm-mm-mmm...
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS growls]
[KRILLIN[ Oh no! Trunks! Get up!
[KRILLIN] No, Trunks!
You can't let him win!
Trunks! Please! Get up!
[TRUNKS groans softly]
[KRILLIN] Huh...?
[KRILLIN] Huh?
[thinking] What is he
trying to tell me?
[KRILLIN thinking] Oh...
Of course! Vegeta!
[thinking] Whoa,
he must be letting Cell
hit him as a distraction!
Guess that's my cue!
[blows landing,
grunting]
[blows landing]
[KRILLIN] This is
for you, Trunks...
[KRILLIN] Vegeta, you helped
Cell become complete
just to satisfy your
own foolish pride...
And look what's happened to you!
Now, Trunks has to fight
that monster all by himself.
Your son is a true hero.
[TRUNKS grunting]
Trunks is giving Cell
everything he's got!
Go on, look!
No! You'll never see
because you've been
blinded by your
own selfish ambition.
I don't know why Trunks
cares so much about you.
But I'm going to keep my
word and get you out of here!
Trunks! I really hope
Vegeta is worth all of this!
Good luck.
[CELL] What's that saying?
"Like father like son?"
Yes! You are as
headstrong as Vegeta,
but soon you'll be wishing
your head was stronger,
when I'm crushing it.
[CELL laughs]
[KRILLIN] Trunks
alone with Cell?!
Aw, I don't like
those odds at all!
[TRUNKS chuckles]
[CELL chuckles]
Looks like you've
saved Vegeta for now!
Huh?!
What? Thought I didn't see, huh?
[TRUNKS growls]
Why'd you let me?
[CELL] Isn't it obvious? I'm
interested in you, not him.
I can kill him any time I want.
[TRUNKS] Not if I can help it!
[CELL] Your loyalty
to your father
is a sign of weakness, Trunks!
It will be your downfall.
[CELL] But enough about
your weakling father.
I'd much rather address
my fight with you.
[TRUNKS growls]
You want me? Come and get me!
I will, but show me more of that
wonderful power of yours first.
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] That's it!
Take your time!
I want you to be at full
strength when I destroy you!
No! This can't be real!
Trunks is going through
an incredible transformation...
His power is now
far greater than Vegeta's!
It's true. I didn't want to
believe it, but I guess there
really is a level beyond
that of a Super Saiyan!
[TRUNKS growls]
[ANDROID 16 thinking]
So this is the boy's secret.
[TRUNKS growls]
[NARRATOR] Fueled by rage, and
ready to sacrifice it all,
Trunks has squared off against
Cell in one final bout.
WIth his energy continuing to
build, Trunks has surpassed
the fighting powers of all the
other heroes!
[TRUNKS growling]
[NARRATOR] Perhaps
his intensive training
in the Hyperbolic Time
Chamber was all he needed?
But Cell is definitely not
going to be defeated easily.
[NARRATOR] Two fighters
from the future throw down
to decide the planet's fate,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!
[TRUNKS yelling]