[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
the wicked Cell Jrs.
drove our heroes
straight into the dirt!
Enduring hit
after brutal hit,
the powerful Z Fighters
were beaten and broken,
left to die in the
lonely desert ring.
Not even Piccolo
or the Super Saiyans
could turn back the
dreadful attackers.
[NARRATOR] With a painful
gasp of realization,
Goku began to think he'd
been wrong about his son.
[NARRATOR] And through all
the horror, Gohan watched!
[CELL] Now take your
anger and feed off of it
before it's too
late for your friends!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Mr. Satan
showed a sliver of courage
as he answered the
body-less 16's plea
and threw him
into the battle,
for the exploded android had one
last message for the young boy.
[ANDROID 16] Gohan, let it go.
I do know how you feel, Gohan,
but it is not a sin to
fight for the right cause
for there are those who
words alone will not reach.
Let it go.
[NARRATOR] And then, with
a swift and fatal step,
16's head was crushed
before Gohan's eyes.
[NARRATOR] And the light of
the gentle Android faded.
[CELL] Yet another fighter
you could have saved.
[NARRATOR] Before his death,
16 asked Gohan to protect
all the life he loved.
To let go of his
restraints and fight.
And now he will.
If there was a button to press,
Cell has pressed it.
If there was a final wall,
Cell has torn it down.
For the gentleness
in Gohan has flown away!
And the power has awoken.
[GOHAN screams]
[NARRATOR] Today,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[GOHAN screams]
[screaming continues]
[CELL chuckles]
[VEGETA gasps]
It's unreal!
This is it!
[GOHAN growls]
[PICCOLO] Gohan's
releasing his energy!
[KRILLIN] G-Gohan...
[GOHAN growling]
That a boy, Gohan.
[CELL laughs]
So, that's it, huh?
[CELL] You are making the
same mistake Trunks did, boy!
Don't think you can
beat me just by powering up.
Huh...?
[CELL JR. 3 giggles]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[screaming]
[KRILLIN yells]
[YAMCHA grunting]
[VEGETA grunts]
[CELL JR. 1 giggles]
[VEGETA yells]
[ANNOUNCER &amp; MR. SATAN whimper]
[GOKU chuckles weakly]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOHAN] Stop it!
Huh...?
[GOHAN] That's enough!!
[screaming]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOHAN] Tell them to stop it!
[CELL gasps]
That's the way.
Let it all go!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN screams]
Incredible!
[screaming continues]
[GOKU chuckles]
Ohhhhh.
Oh no, this whole
place is gonna blow!
[screaming]
[CROWD gasping]
[BOTH gasp]
[CHICHI screams]
[OX-KING yells]
[MR. SATAN groans,
ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[VEGETA gasps]
[CELL JR. 7 gasps]
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOHAN] I can never forgive
you for what you've done!
[CELL stammers]
[CELL gasps]
[CELL] At last you've
come out of hiding.
Now the game will
really get exciting!
[GOHAN] No games.
[CELL gasps]
H-How did you?!
[CELL] The Senzu Beans!
How did you get them?!
[CELL growls]
[growling]
[screaming]
[CELL gasps]
After all the time we've spent
trying to kill these things,
he does it in one blow!
[TRUNKS] Gohan, you're amazing!
[GOKU chuckles weakly]
I told you so!
[PICCOLO grunts]
G-Gohan...
[CELL JRs. gasp]
[CELL gasps]
But how...?!
He's so fast!
He did it right!
He increased his strength
without losing speed!
[BOTH growl]
[giggling]
[giggling continues]
[BOTH gasp]
[CELL JR. 6 growls]
Gohan... Don't worry about me...
Just do what'cha gotta do!
Do it, Gohan!
[CELL JR. 6 gasps]
[GOHAN snarls]
I-I can't believe
what I'm seeing!
[GOKU chuckles weakly]
[CELL growls]
[CHICHI] Wh-What happened...?
[OX-KING] ChiChi!
Oh good, you're alright!
Did anything happen
to my precious Gohan?!
Please, you've have to tell me!
I don't know.
He was building up his power and
then the TV went on the fritz!
Oh, my brave, little warrior!
He's too young to be fighting!
He should be at home studying!
But no, he had to listen
to his father instead of me!
Hey!
Your son Gohan
is no longer a baby!
Why, he's transcended Goku
and he's become
an honorable warrior!
I know it's hard
for you to accept,
but both your husband
and son are battling
to save this entire planet!
Without them, we're gone!
Oh sure, I wish it was
me instead of him,
but Gohan is the
only hope we have left!
C'mon, ChiChi.
Everything will be okay.
[CHICHI] Is there more?
Or are you done preaching to me?
[OX-KING whimpers]
But, ChiChi--!
[OX-KING gasps]
[CHICHI growls]
Get out of here!
[CHICHI grunts]
[OX-KING gasps]
You're saying
I don't know my own son?!
You think just
by saving the Earth,
he'll be able to get
into a good school?!
And then what? You think he'll
be able to get a descent job?!
You're the one
who doesn't have a clue!
[OX-KING] Alright, ChiChi,
just calm down!
[CHICHI] You want ME
to calm down?!
Someone else can fight
those stupid battles!
I just don't want
him to be a hooligan!
Goku, you bring me
back my baby right now!
Huh...?
[thinking] So this is the power
Goku was bragging about!
Hmph!
Well, let's just see it
against all five of them!
[GOHAN yells]
[grunting]
[GOHAN grunts]
No one's watching me!
Don't they realize that
I'm the real star of this show?!
I'm the one who threw
that guy's head over there!
This is all because of me!
He... could win!
I don't believe it!
Ladies and gentlemen,
that brave little kid
is fighting a valiant battle
against a throng of
blood thirsty Mini-Cells!
Hey, would you keep
rolling you amateur?!
B-But I can't! It's all broken!
Well, fix it then!
Don't you realize we're missing
the scoop of the century?!
[growling]
[screaming]
[GOHAN yells]
[grunting]
[VEGETA] He just blew all
those creatures off
with nothing but his energy!
[TRUNKS] And look at him!
He's perfectly calm!
It's like he hasn't
even warmed up yet!
Goku, are you okay?
Uhh, yeah...
[PICCOLO grunts]
Didn't I tell you so?
He's going to do it, Piccolo.
[GOKU chuckles]
[PICCOLO growls]
Gohan...
[screaming]
[CELL JR.] Destructo-Disc!
[CELL JR.] Kamehame... HA!
[CELL JR.] Special beam cannon!
Tri-Beam... HA!
[CELL JR. gasps]
[GOHAN screams]
[CELL JRs. screaming]
I said before, I could
never forgive you!
[GOHAN growls]
[CELL JR. screams]
[GOHAN grunts]
[CELL JR. gasps]
[CELL JR. grunts]
[CELL snarls]
[growling]
Look at what you've done!
[PICCOLO] Nothing is
holding Gohan back now.
He's finally learned how to
tap into his power at will!
Now it's time to pay, Cell.
You're going to
face up to your crimes.
Pass these around, Trunks!
Huh...?
Sure.
[CELL gasps]
[CELL growls]
[NARRATOR] And so, the
demonstration has been made!
After releasing his
incredible hidden power,
Gohan has erased all seven
of the vicious Cell Jrs.
without the
slightest difficulty.
Now he moves to a
bigger and better enemy:
the mighty Cell himself!
Are the predictions
of Goku correct?
Can Gohan indeed
put an end to Cell
and all of his
tormenting games?
Has the role of the planet's
protector been passed on
from father... to son?
The climactic battle begins,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!