[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
there was a festive gathering
at Master Roshi's
and Gohan didn't want
to miss out on the fun.
So he snuck away from his house
without his mom's permission.
Let's blaze. What'dya say?
[chuckles lowly]
Shh!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Kami's Lookout was under siege.
And when Mr. Popo tried
to make a run for it,
he was ensnared in a net.
[[WARRIORS laugh]
[MR. POPO] Magic carpet!
[BOTH] Righ, Boss! Huah!
[NARRATOR]
To add to his humiliation,
and to Kami's anger,
Garlic Jr. reduced
Mr. Popo to pocket size.
Don't have a
heart attack, old man.
I don't want
you to die before...
[NARRATOR] But Kami wasn't
going to take this sitting down.
It was an all out war
against the greedy ghoul.
But after a sneak attack
by Garlic Jr.'s henchmen,
Kami was captured, and, he too,
was reduced to the size
of an action-figure.
[NARRATOR] It was a dark day
for the earth indeed,
when Garlic Jr. uncorked
the dreaded Black Water Mist.
[GARLIC JR.] When people breath
this mist, any evil tendencies
that they're resisting take
control of their character.
You see, boys,
our army of darkness
has always been here.
We just have to wake it up.
Yeah. You've really outdone
yourself this time, Boss.
[GARLIC JR.] Why thank you.
[NARRATOR] What sinister
plan does Garlic Jr.
have in store for the earth?
Find out, today!
[birds chirping]
[GIRL] Oh no.
What's wrong with me?
I feel so... I feel...
[screeches]
[GARLIC JR.] The Black Water
Mist has been released
upon the earth, Father.
Just as you would have wanted.
They're weak, so weak,
these Earthlings.
Like sheep, lost sheep,
without the strength of will
to resist the dark side.
[GARLIC JR.] They only
need a ruler, Father,
to lead them further and
further into the darkness.
[laughs]
And they'll have one,
when I wish you back.
[GARLIC JR.]
What's taking so long, Spice?
[SPICE] Lord. Please
be patient with me.
[GARLIC JR.] More waiting?
I've waited too long already.
How hard could it be to find
a kid with that fancy mirror?
What are you looking at,
you boobs?
I'll bet you two
know who I'm looking for.
For the ones responsible for
locking me in the Dead Zone.
Hm!
[GARLIC JR.] Goku and his
little runt, Gohan. Mmm.
[CHICHI] Gohan?! Gohan.
Where are you?!
You'd better get over
here this instant.
Uh! Gohan, how could you?! Ah!
It's Krillin and
those friends of his.
I'll bet they talked him
into doing this.
Are those silly karate bums
ever going to grow up?
Life is not just an interval
between Kung Fu matches?!
[CHICHI yells]
[GOHAN laughs]
How great. Getting to see
everybody again. Man.
[GOHAN] Ha, ha, ha.
Whoa. Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ahhh. That was great, Icarus.
Ah...
[birds cawing]
Hm?!
Huh?!
[commotion]
[GOHAN] Ooh, that doesn't
look good, Icarus. Be careful.
Whoa. Let's get outta here.
Don't touch it.
[ICARUS bleats]
[GOHAN] Whoa! Hey!
Ow! He bucked me. Like a bronc'.
[GOHAN] I wonder what that
stuff was?! It was horrible.
[ICARUS mutters]
It's gone now. Hm?
[GOHAN] Oh. Hello.
[snarls]
Ahhh. Hey, there.
[screeches]
Huh?! Waaaa.
Huh?!
[snarling and growling]
Icarus. Easy, boy.
There's too many of them.
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN] Icarus, jump.
Oh, man. Whoa. What's up?!
They're freaking.
Gosh. How weird. Man.
[GOHAN] I thought I was
gonna lose you, Icarus.
[snarls]
Easy there, Popo.
You might as well
conserve your energy.
That was try number
ninety-six, wasn't it?!
No. Seven. Please, one more.
I just can't sit here and wait.
If everyone breathes the mist,
[MR. POPO] there'll be
no one left to help.
Yes. I'm afraid
you're right, Mr. Popo.
I should have seen this coming.
[KAMI] Garlic Jr.
and his father, Garlic,
seek only to destabilize.
Their bitter pledge
is to make Earth a home
for the serpent race.
A race of spirits who work
for their own satisfaction
out of pride and lack of love.
They are blind, Mr. Popo.
They have forgotten that
they too have a part to play
in the Grand Design,
so they seek to tear it down.
And so they march,
time and time again,
with every age and every
epoch, doomed to failure.
Destined to become victims
of the very seeds of discord
that they, themselves,
have sown.
[screams]
[KAMI] But they've got a firm
foothold this time, Mr. Popo.
And it's going to take some
real doing to stop them.
I only wish Goku were here.
Yes, he would stop them
in their tracks.
[gasps]
[SPICE] Sir, it's the kid.
We found him.
Huh?! Show me.
[SPICE] At least I think
it's him, Lord Garlic.
[giggles]
Yes, it's him. Good.
All right, boys,
go get that kid.
Then we won't need to find Goku.
Yes. He'll come walking
right into our hands.
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[ROSHI giggles]
[KRILLIN yells]
[laughing]
Yo, good job.
They're laughing at you.
You're really making their day.
[YAMCHA] Try using the
pointy end, Krillin.
Yo. Why don't you get out here
and try, big mouth.
Hey, forget it.
I'm not the one
who promised Maron
we were having fish
for dinner. Remember?!
[BOTH laugh]
[MARON] Krillin!
[BOTH] Huh?
Hey. I'll help you.
Look out, fish! Here I come!
Oh my gosh.
[ROSHI] Oh, ho, ho yeah!
Come to papa, baby.
[ROSHI] Old Roshi's got
something to show ya.
[laughs]
[MARON] Hey, Krillin.
What's the deal?
You're not giving up, are you?!
Well, are you?!
No way.
Yo! Heads up!
Huh?!
[KRILLIN yells]
[ROSHI yells]
Man overboard.
All right, guys.
Where is Gohan?! Answer me!
Uh, he's... not here.
Fine. I'll wait then.
Good. Fortunately
it's not too late
to nip this in the bud.
He doesn't need any
bad influences right now.
What?! Bad influence?!
ChiChi, these guys
saved the planet.
Yeah. So?
Come on! Loosen up!
[gasps] Who are you?!
A friend. I was invited here.
But I don't think you were!
[grunts]
All right, you!
You'd better stay out of this!
[MARON giggles]
You're just a jealous old lady.
[ALL] Uh...
You should go home.
Your grandson's obviously
not here right now.
[giggles]
But I can see why
he needed to get away.
Why you...!
That does it. I hope
you like black and blue
'cause you're gonna be
wearing it for a while.
[ROSHI] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
ChiChi, please.
Control yourself.
She doesn't know any better.
She didn't mean it.
Hey! Watch it! You're even
worse than the old lady.
[CHICHI] Why you little!
Hey Krillin!
C'mon, Maron. Hurry. Let's go.
Okay. Bye, Grandma.
Don't come back.
That's it! She's dead!
Someone needs to
teach that vixen a lesson.
[CHICHI] Let go!
[ROSHI hollers, giggles]
[CHICHI] Let me go!
I'll step on your feet!
That girl's history!
This isn't fair! Let me go!
[CHICHI] Let go!
Babe, you gotta be more careful.
Who, me?!
Yeah, you. That's not
an ordinary lady
you're looking at there.
[KRILLIN] ChiChi's one of the
strongest women on the planet.
Even Goku's afraid of her.
You've mentioned
him before. Who is he?!
He's my friend. The one
from outer-space, remember?!
I told you about ten times!
Whatever.
Krillin...!
[CHICHI] Let go of me!
Somebody's got to
teach that girl some manners!
Ugh! What a fool!
I've never met anyone
that acted like that before.
What a spoiled, little brat!
[gasps]
[CHICHI screams]
[chuckles]
Y'know what?! They're going
to be surprised to see me! Ha!
[GOHAN] What's up, boy?!
[MARON] Gotcha.
Ahhh. Hey, guys.
Huh?
Gohan. All right!
Yeah! See. I made it.
Awesome. You're great.
[GOHAN] Thanks, Maron.
Don't mention it, kid.
I like your friend,
he's really cute.
Don't you think? Huh?
Uhh, cute? Well, I... guess so.
Hey, Gohan, there's trouble
afoot, bro. Your ma's here.
Huh?! Oh no, my mom? Bummer!
Boy, yeah. I feel
sorry for you, Gohan.
Yeah, whoa.
She's gone ballistic.
Mhmm.
Oh, man.
[MARON] Here I come!
Huh?!
Hi, what's you're name?
Hey, I know how you can
get these guys off the hook.
Take the blame! Go tell her
that it's your fault.
What?! Me?!
Are you out of your mind?!
I don't have a death wish!
Oh, I get it now.
You don't really respect me.
You think I'm dumb.
No, no I don't.
Then you'll try my idea?!
Oh, all right.
I'll take the fall, Gohan.
Wow. What a friend. Thank you.
Krillin, you're great! Wow!
[MARON] Where is everybody?!
[KRILLIN]
I guess they're all inside.
Chin up, kid.
Okay, Krillin. Get ready.
Mm.
[KRILLIN] I don't know, guys.
I got a funny
feeling about this.
[growls]
Huh?!
Uhhh. Mom, what's up?!
It's my fault, ChiChi.
I-I'm sorry.
I talked Gohan
into coming here.
Gosh, Mom. I'm really sorry.
I was wrong. Hm?!
Ahh. Gohan, are you okay?!
Hey, you better
back off there, Grandma.
Oh, boy o' boy.
[KRILLIN] Gosh, ChiChi,
that was pretty severe.
[breathy hiss]
Gosh, Mom.
[GOHAN] Yikes!
Aaah...
Oh. Maron! Now you
got her all fired-up
with that Grandma stuff.
Yeah, but she hit him.
[CHICHI grunting]
[KRILLIN] Oh! Thank goodness.
It's going to take all of us
to stop her this time, guys!
She's really flipped!
Whoa. I'm sorry, Mom.
I'll be a good boy
from now on, I promise.
I'll study hard
and I'll do everything
[GOHAN] that you tell me to do.
Mom, what's wrong?
You've never tried to
[GOHAN]
hurt me like this before.
Ahhh! Get away fom me, you!
[yelling]
Krillin! Help me!
I'm trying, Maron. But I kind
of have my hands full here.
Guys? If we've offended you
somehow, we're really sorry.
Something's not right here, man.
They're freakin' out.
Huh?!
Man. What in the world
is going on here?
[growling]
[BOTH grunting]
[thud]
Oh no, Mom.
I hope you're not hurt.
Man, Krillin!
They mean business, Gohan.
Be careful or they'll hurt you.
[GOHAN]
Mom, what's wrong with you?
[KRILLIN] Gohan, look out!
[GOHAN]
What are we going to do?
[screams]
[ROSHI] Come here, my dear.
There's nothing to be scared of.
[MARON yells]
[chuckles]
[yells]
[MARON crying]
[KRILLIN] It's okay, Maron.
You're fine.
[WARRIORS chuckle]
[VINEGAR] Party's over, kiddo.
Oh, great. Who are these goons?
Huh?! Mom, what are
you doing? Get up.
[GOHAN] Guys, what's going on?
[MUSTARD] They inhaled
the Black Water Mist, kid.
They belong to us now.
[GOHAN] Oh, no they don't.
That's my mom.
And those are our friends.
They belong to us.
[SALT] Why don't you ask them?
Gohan, wait.
No. I'm not scared. These freaks
did something to my mom.
We sure did. So?
So you'd better
change her back right now.
[SALT chuckles]
We can't, you dope.
Only the Sacred Water kept
at Kami's Lookout can do that.
Sacred Water?
That's right. But Kami's on
an extended leave of absence.
Too bad, aye? But don't worry.
Our boss is
guardian now. Garlic Jr.
[SPICE] Oh, I see
you remember him.
Lord Garlic will be pleased.
Yes, indeed he will.
Give up, kid.
You're outnumbered.
[yells]
[SPICE] It's no use, kid.
The more you struggle,
the tighter the hold becomes.
It's hard to believe
that a small-fry like you
trapped Garlic Jr.
in the Dead Zone.
[laughs]
Piccolo.
Yes! Piccolo!
[chuckles]
Good. Yeah, this'll be fun.
Fun? You slither around
in the darkness,
waiting to capitalize
on people's weaknesses.
And you call that fun?
[SALT] Garlic Jr. can
destroy you anytime, Piccolo.
He has Kami held captive,
you fool.
What? Garlic Jr.'s back?
[PICCOLO] Oh, great.
[NARRATOR] As Piccolo
prepares to defend himself
against this posse of darkness,
Garlic Jr.'s
stranglehold on the earth
seems to be getting
tighter and tighter.
On the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!