[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta made a
devastating attack
that blew the seemingly
invincible Majin Buu
to smithereens!
[KRILLIN yells]
[NARRATOR] It was an attack
that left the Saiyan Prince
without any life force
of his own.
The once cold-hearted Vegeta
had made the
ultimate sacrifice,
extinguishing his own life in
an attempt to rid the Earth
of the evil Majin Buu
once and for all...
[NARRATOR] The solitary warrior
fell to a stony death,
leaving nothing behind except
the hope that Buu was finished;
that the creature
would trouble his family
and friends no more.
[NARRATOR] But when Piccolo
arrived at the scene,
he found that the
elastic remnants
of Majin Buu were
far from dead.
The Namek could only
look on in horror
at the amazing resurrection
of the unstoppable Buu.
[NARRATOR]
In a bubblegum-like frenzy,
the terrifying nemesis reformed
into his original shape,
fully rejuvenated.
[BUU]
Buuuuu.
[BABIDI whimpers]
[NARRATOR] Not fairing so well
was the wicked Babidi
who angrily commanded
Buu to use his powers
to restore him
back to full health.
[NARRATOR] And the duo of
darkness was back in action,
ready to wreak havoc on the
inhabitants of Earth once again.
[BABIDI] There'll be no quick
end for those scoundrels.
[NARRATOR]
Elsewhere, deep in the forest,
Gohan barely clings to life.
But can anything prevent
the young warrior
from crossing through
death's door?
[YAMCHA]
Six down and one to go.
At least the Dragon Ball
hunting's going well.
[ROSHI] That's right. And, uh,
do you think we can pull over?
I, uh, need a break.
I had a lot to drink...
[VIDEL]
I just hope these things work.
Oh, they work. You don't have
to worry about that, Videl.
That's good.
But, hey, shouldn't
we be looking for
Trunks and Goten, you guys?
Isn't that a
little more important
than finding the Dragon Balls?
[CHICHI]
Huh. What do you think, Bulma?
I don't know, but Trunks and
Goten could be anywhere.
At least with
the Dragon Balls
we know we're
accomplishing something.
And besides, I wanna
wish the people that
Vegeta killed in the
stadium back to life.
I owe it to them. That was
a terrible thing Vegeta did.
We should be getting
pretty close, huh?
What d'you say one hour?
Mm-hmm. We're close. Just keep
heading in this direction.
I'd say another
15 minutes or so.
Bulma, be truthful:
Is one of the reasons
that you're so intent on
gathering Dragon Balls,
well, you know, that something's
happened to the boys?
No, I think the boys
are okay, ChiChi.
For some reason I haven't
been too worried about that.
I did get a sick feeling in my
heart about Vegeta though.
He might need to be
wished back to life,
but I don't think I
want to wish him back.
Unless... he's back
to the way he was.
Don't worry, Bulma.
He'll be fine.
Vegeta's not one to
be controlled.
I hope you're right.
Hey, we've got an
exact fix on that last ball.
Steady as she goes, Yamcha.
[YAMCHA]
Right.
It's kind of hard to believe
that you can actually
wish people back from the
dead with these things.
Well, look at me.
I was as dead as you can get,
and I was wished back to life.
[BULMA] Don't worry, Videl.
Most people come back normal.
[YAMCHA] Hey! What's that
supposed to mean?!
[BULMA]
Slow down, Yamcha.
It must be on that
little island over there.
The Dragon Radar says
that it's at sea level.
That's got to be it.
[YAMCHA]
Okay. Here we go.
[ALL scream]
[BULMA]
What the heck was that, Yamcha?!
[YAMCHA] Hey, that was a
difficult landing!
[BULMA] Especially if you
don't know how to land!
[ALL grunt]
[ANDROID 18] Hey, the plane has
settled. You can get up now.
Hey, thank you so much!
My head almost hit the wall!
I think you may
have saved my life!
I was thrown viciously,
just like this!
But I hit something soft instead
of the wall. It was you!
I don't know
how I can repay you!
I could've cracked
my head open!
But this is so soft and
nice... Thank you so much...
[ROSHI grunts]
Let go! Please! I was only
trying to show you something!
How to be a lecherous old man.
No. I was just
trying to show you
how these flotation
devices saved my life!
[ROSHI squeals]
[YAJIROBE] Are you sure that
you sensed someone coming?
I don't see anybody.
Huh?
Hey, what's up with
the runts, you guys?
Hey. Do you have any
more Senzu Beans?
We're not running a
bean factory here!
You just took our last three!
We're gonna have
to start charging.
I'm surprised that you haven't
started charging already,
knowing you!
Hey! What do you mean by that?!
I live like a monk up here!
I don't even have a TV set!
You don't have a TV? Wow!
You really are roughing it up
here. Let's vamoose, Piccolo.
[YAJIROBE] That's right!
All I do is grow beans
for you ingrates! I can't even
get a pizza delivered up here!
[KRILLIN]
If you weren't so lazy,
you could learn how to fly!
[YAJIROBE thinking]
Hey, he's right.
I could fly my own pizzas up.
[MR. POPO]
It's Piccolo!
[DENDE]
And Krillin!
[MR. POPO]
Hello, up there!
[DENDE] How are you doing?
It's good to see you again.
Uh-oh. It looks like Trunks
and Goten are injured.
Please don't tell me
the boys have been hurt.
No, they're fine.
Vegeta just knocked them out
so they wouldn't interfere.
They just need to rest
for a little while.
[MR. POPO]
Oh, thank goodness.
Then we should get
them to bed. Popo?
Yes, sir.
I just watched the
sheets yesterday.
And I put fresh pillow cases
on them this morning.
Let's see... They can
use Kami's old quilt!
Yes, that's the
softest one we've got.
[DENDE]
Thanks, Mr. Popo.
[MR. POPO]
My pleasure.
So then, I take it we haven't
made any headway
against Buu and Babidi?
Mm. I'm afraid not. We've been
pounded so far. Even Goku.
[DENDE]
I know it's been hard.
I've been sensing
the whole battle.
You have? Then you can tell us
how Goku's doing! Is he okay?!
Well, it is difficult to kill
a man who's already dead.
[laughs]
Yeah. I guess you've
got a point there.
[laughs]
[KRILLIN gasps]
A little while ago,
Vegeta's energy signal
completely disappeared.
Yeah, he's gone.
His attack had Buu
into a million pieces,
but Buu just reformed.
How do you beat an
enemy that can do that?
It doesn't seem possible.
Hey. What about Gohan?
Mmm... I can't sense
him. I'm sorry.
Gohan...
Dende. What about the Supreme
Kai? Can you still sense him?
Oh no. I forgot about Supreme
Kai. I'll try to find him.
[PICCOLO] Good.
There's no way to make a plan
until we figure out who
we have left to work with.
I sense him! You can sense
him, too. Just look with me.
Yes. I feel it! It's faint,
but it's still there!
Buu's power must have
been masking it!
[DENDE] Piccolo, tell me.
Do we have a chance?
Given what we have and
what we're up against,
I'd say no.
But nothings certain.
Ever since I saw Goku transform
into a Super Saiyan,
I don't rule anything out.
[DENDE]
I understand.
You're saying we need
a miracle to win.
But that you've seen
one happen before.
[PICCOLO]
Yes.
So? Would someone tell me
where the heck we go from here?
[MR. POPO] If I were you,
I'd do what Goku would do.
He'd eat the meal I just
pulled out of the oven
rather than fight
on an empty stomach.
[stomach growls]
[chuckles]
Why not? Let's eat.
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN]
Hey, wait up!
[thinking] Gohan, have you
really left us, my friend?
I can't feel it in my heart.
[SUPREME KAI grunts]
Gohan! You have to be alive!
We can't do this without you...
You have got to hold on!
[grunts]
[SUPREME KAI] I will not...
give up... until I find you.
[SUPREME KAI grunts]
[SUPREME KAI]
Gohan...
[BABIDI] Yes. This will
be a fine city to destroy.
[BABIDI giggles]
[BABIDI] This is great!
Babidi and Buu. Unstoppable!
[BABIDI giggles]
[screams]
[BABIDI]
Majin Buu! What are you doing?!
You see that, don't you?! Buu?!
[screams]
[BABIDI] What are you doing?!
Look out! We're going to crash!
[BUU giggles]
[BABIDI]
Are you nuts?!
Don't ever pull a
crazy stunt like that again!
Ah! Look! I'm bleeding!
I've got a paper cut!
[BULMA]
There you are.
Hey, guys!
I found it but I can't reach it!
How about some help up here?!
[YAMCHA] No deal! You said you
wanted to do it on your own!
Remember? And "get
some aggression out."
[growls]
[BULMA thinking] If I get my
hands on that Dragon Ball,
the first thing I'm going to do
is throw it at Yamcha's head!
[BULMA grunts]
Hey, Bulma! Little stuck?!
Give her a break.
She's a mother, you know.
Doing great! Come on, old gal!
"Old gal"?!
She'd better watch it...
[BULMA grunts]
[BULMA thinking]
Almost there.
[YAMCHA gasps]
[thinking]
Just a little bit more...
[BULMA]
Whoa!
Hey, what's the--?! Ooh?!
[screams]
[BULMA thinking] All right,
Bulma, stay calm!
[screams]
Bulma!
[DRAGON roars]
[BULMA whimpers]
[screams]
Huh? Hey.. Give us back our
Dragon Ball right this second!
Do you hear me?! Cough it up,
you overgrown beast!
Hey! Come back! That's ours!
No fair! We found it first!
Yaah!
[DRAGON roars]
[YAMCHA]
Bull's eye!
You idiot! What do you
think you're doing?!
Go after him! We need
that Dragon Ball!
[YAMCHA]
Right! I'm on it!
[YAMCHA gasps]
Or not. That's one
heck of a jump there!
Hey, these clothes
are expensive,
I'm not jumping in there!
[BULMA] What kind of
lame excuse is that?!
Just take them off
and go in your underwear!
See, uh, that poses a problem.
Ah, I'm not wearing any.
Yeah, right. I bet
you're just chickening out?
Hmm. What about you?
[coughs] Yeah, I'd definitely go
if I didn't have this cold!
[BULMA]
The men are scared.
Well, I'm not.
But I don't feel like
getting wet right now. So no.
At least you
were honest about it,
unlike certain others I know!
ChiChi! How 'bout it?!
[CHICHI] All right,
you cowards! I'll do it!
[gasps]
Hey, don't get killed!
Gohan would never forgive me!
Gotta admit that girl is brave.
[thinking]
Huh? Oh, great!
Well, I've had it!
If no one else is going to
help that courageous girl,
then I will!
If all else fails, they
nail you with the guilt.
And now Bulma's going to give me
grief for lying to her!
Oh, well. Here goes!
[DRAGON growls]
[CHICHI thinking]
You're not getting away
with that Dragon Ball!
Not while I'm here, buster!
[YAMCHA thinking]
Oh no you don't!
These are my favorite
underwear, buddy!
[ROSHI] Hm? [coughs]
I hope they're okay! [coughs]
[MARON]
That's a mean monster!
Do you think they
need help, Mommy?
[ROSHI screams]
[laughs]
[ANDROID 18]
Yes, sugar.
It looks like Master Roshi's
going to handle it.
[ROSHI screaming]
[DRAGON roars]
No! He's gonna eat Roshi!
[screams]
[ROSHI]
Sorry, world.
[farting]
[DRAGON gags]
[CHICHI grunts]
Eugh!
[YAMCHA]
Ew! Rancid!
[VIDEL]
Gross! How disgusting!
[ALL retch]
[DRAGON coughs]
Ha, ha! Bulls eye!
I've still got it, baby!
[ROSHI grunts]
[YAMCHA] That was definitely
one for the record books.
Good going, Master Roshi!
What an attack.
You saved the day!
I know we usually give
you a lot of grief,
but being a dirty old man
paid off this time.
Hey, yeah... [chuckles]
[ALL laugh]
[BUU giggles]
[BABIDI] It's a great day to
wreak havoc, isn't it Majin Buu?
--[BUU giggles]
--[train horn blares]
Majin Buu, go to the left
or we're going to be hit!
All right. If you don't
want to go left, go right!
Just get out of the way!
Majin Buu! Are you listening?!
[GOKU grunts]
[thinking] Man, I feel like
I was run over by a train.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah, now
I remember. Vegeta...
Figures, first the
guy knocks me out cold,
and then he has to take the
last Senzu Bean for himself.
[GOKU grunts]
[VEGETA]
So Kakarot,
even you can prove helpless
when you drop your guard.
[thinking] Hmm... I wonder
how the others are doing?
I can still sense Buu,
but I can't sense
Vegeta or Gohan either!
This isn't good...
Man, how long was
I out for? Too long...
Something's happened,
something terrible.
Oh! It feels like Piccolo and
Krillin are back in action.
They probably know
what's going on.
Gohan. I'm sorry
I wasn't there for you.
[KRILLIN]
We're in a real dilemma here.
Gohan and Vegeta are dead.
Goku isn't
anywhere to be found!
H-How could it get any worse?
[PICCOLO] We've been in
tough situations before.
Yeah, I know,
b-but Goku always showed up
when things got really bad.
Like they are now...
Sorry, guys. I should
be more positive.
That's the way Goku would be!
[PICCOLO]
Goku knows that to win,
you have to believe
that you're going to win.
[KRILLIN]
Yeah, he's like a little kid.
He thinks he can do anything.
Hey, speaking of kids,
do you think it be all right
if I brought my
family up here, Dende?
[DENDE] I'm not sure.
What do you think?
You're the Guardian of the
Earth, now. It's your decision.
Well, technically speaking,
it's not proper.
But, if it wasn't for you guys,
this planet wouldn't even
be here, so I say,
let's bend the rules.
Hey, great!
Thanks a lot, Dende!
Huh?!
Yeah! I feel it, too!
[KRILLIN]
I'm either hallucinating
or that's Goku standing there!
Goku, is that really you?
Hi.
He's real! He talks
and everything!
[laughs]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Hey, what's the deal?
Why are you so sad?
I thought you'd be
happy to see me!
I'm not sad, you oaf!
I'm just so happy
that I could cry!
You're alive! You're alive!
[GOKU] Well, I'm about as
alive as a dead guy can be.
[KRILLIN]
Look at you.
You look like you've been
through a meat grinder!
How 'bout we get those
injuries taken care of?
Ahh. A Senzu Bean, huh?
No, we're out! But we can
do better than that! Heh, heh.
That is if Dende's willing
to do some healing.
What d'ya say,
Guardian of the Earth?
[DENDE]
Well, of course. Certainly.
[GOKU] Wow, thank you.
I really appreciate it.
[DENDE] Don't mention it.
I'm honored to be able to help.
[NARRATOR] As the weights
of pain and fatigue
are lifted from
Goku's shoulders,
his mission becomes
more and more clear.
With fire in his eyes,
the Super Saiyan has
only one thing on his mind.
Ridding the Earth
of the evil Majin Buu!