[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
deep in Majin Buu's head,
Goku and Vegeta found the pods
that housed the
captured Z Fighters.
And they made another
startling discovery as well.
[VEGETA] You don't like
that idea, do you?
Huh? Majin Buu!
In his original form!
[VEGETA] Yes, I see that.
But what does it mean?
[GOKU] Who knows?
How could he absorb himself?
Doesn't make sense.
Wow. This is deep.
Two Buus. Strange.
Maybe there were two Buus at
one time and this one lost.
[NARRATOR]
Unlikely? Yes. But true!
There had been more
than one Majin Buu.
And as Goku and Vegeta
unraveled the mystery,
the merciless pink monster
decided to make a
special guest appearance
inside his own mind.
[SUPER BUU] Who are you calling
"ugly", you ridiculous fool?
[NARRATOR] It was an
all-or-nothing battle,
but, coupled together,
it looked like Saiyan
might had prevailed
and the two warriors astutely
disposed of the last remains
of the Buu within Buu.
[NARRATOR] It was a job
well done to be sure,
but was Majin Buu
really gone for good?
[SUPER BUU]
Knock, knock.
[VEGETA]
Who's there?
[SUPER BUU]
Buu.
Buu who?
[SUPER BUU] Aw. Don't cry.
Everyone has to die sometime.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[NARRATOR]
It was a rude awakening,
but the Super Saiyan duo
was realizing the hard way
that the worst place
to fight Majin Buu
is inside of his head--
where his slightest
whim can become reality.
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR] Is the Saiyan
prince bound to become
just another hero in a pod
like the other tenants
in Buu's hall of
living collectibles?
[GOKU]
No!
[NARRATOR]
Stay tuned.
Ahh...
He'll bring much power...
Vegeta! Get up!
[GOKU]
Oh, no you don't!
[SUPER BUU growls]
[yells]
[GOKU yells, grunts]
[chuckles]
This is where you freaks
become a part of me.
[screams]
[yells, laughs]
[SUPER BUU]
Scared you, didn't I?!
No!
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[SUPER BUU]
Denied!
Where did he go?
[GOKU gasps]
That's it. Keep it up.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
You will eventually
wear yourself out.
But don't worry. You'll get
plenty of rest in your pod.
No way. Not me. You'll never
get me into one of those things.
[chuckles]
Oh, no? Well,
half of me believes you,
but the other half?
Well, that's another story.
[GOKU grunts]
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[OLD KAI yells]
Darn it! I want to see inside!
[OLD KAI whines]
[KIBITO KAI thinking]
I pray that you're holding up
better than my ancestor.
[SUPER BUU]
You've missed me, haven't you?
[GOKU grunts]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[growls]
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[SUPER BUU] Too bad.
It's almost over, isn't it?
I must say...
that I am impressed, though.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
You've lasted pretty long.
How a weakling like you still
has energy left is beyond me.
Yeah, well. I don't expect you
to be able to comprehend me.
[GOKU growls]
Missed!
[laughs]
[SUPER BUU] Come on. Lousy aim!
What are you shooting at?!
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Hi.
[chuckles]
I can't help but noticing you
lack the power to destroy me.
[laughs]
[GOKU growls]
[growls]
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[chuckles]
This won't hurt that bad.
[VEGETA] I'd get away
from him if I were you.
Huh?!
You've got bigger
things to worry about.
[VEGETA] Like what will happen
if I yank this thing down.
[SUPER BUU gasps]
Oh, you don't like
that idea do you now?
[SUPER BUU whimpers]
[VEGETA]
I didn't think so.
I wonder what you'd turn into
without this fat tub
of lard in your system?
Whatever it is,
I'm sure it won't be pretty.
[SUPER BUU]
No! Put that down!
Come now, you're not
really in a position
to be giving me orders,
now are you?
[SUPER BUU]
You don't understand!
Let go of that! Now!!
Oh, I think I
understand just perfectly.
The writing's on
the wall now, Majin Buu.
[chuckles]
Stop that right now!!
[VEGETA]
I don't understand.
First, you're laughing at me
with that ridiculous laugh,
and now, now you're yelling
at me at the top of your lungs.
Didn't anyone
teach you any manners?
Please! Let go! If you
tear those attachments
I won't be me anymore!
You won't be you anymore?
That sounds interesting.
Let's give it a try, shall we?
Nooooooo!!
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[yells]
[gasps, grunts]
He might resurface again.
He's always managed
to do it before.
Rest easy, Kakarot.
That Buu's gone for good.
[screams]
[SUPER BUU screams]
Oh, brother. I wonder what
in the world got under his skin?
Gosh. I don't know.
[screaming]
What are you doing?!
Idiot! It's time to
grab the pods and run. Let's go!
Oh, right.
[screams]
[screaming continues]
Hey! Which way is out?!
Who knows?!
[growls]
[gasps]
[GOKU] Either I'm hallucinating
or this whole place is changing.
Yes, Buu's body is morphing.
We've got to get out!
[screams]
Hey. Why is it suddenly
burning up in this place?
It feels like
we're inside a volcano!
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
Wait! Take a look!
[VEGETA]
This whole place is erupting!
Kakarot, you were right.
It's exactly like
a volcano in here.
And at this rate we'll
all be cooked alive!
[screams]
[gasps]
[yelps]
Kakarot!
[GOKU whimpers]
[VEGETA]
What are you doing?!
What do you think?! I'm trying
to cool my self off! Jeez!
[VEGETA]
What's going on down there?
[GOKU]
Nothing good. That's for sure.
[GOKU screams,
VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] What the...?!
Whoa, d'you feel that heat?!
No kidding! Scorching...
That would melt the
skin right off your bones!
That steam's
hotter than lava. Wow!
Wait. This steam is rising,
which means it's
trying to find a way out.
This might lead us out of here!
Check it out. More holes.
[VEGETA]
Is that daylight?
[GOKU]
That would be a miracle.
But then again,
I never rule those out.
[VEGETA]
Let's go!
Hey, it is. All right!
It's closing!
Come on!
[VEGETA snarls]
[VEGETA]
You've got to be kidding me!
[GOKU]
Man! We almost had it!
[screams]
Open... Sesame!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA]
Genius...
It's not working. We've got
to think of something else.
There is no "something else."
Maybe if it happened once,
it'll happen again.
Hey, you're right. Remember?
Buu's thoughts. We saw it
when we read his mind.
Every time he got mad
he kept blowing his stack.
That was it! The steam we saw!
So what's next?
Just hold on to these
and I'll do the rest.
[GOKU]
All right. Here we go.
Show time!
[GOKU grunts]
Ready?!
[VEGETA]
It's not open yet.
Now! It's open!
[GOKU]
Haaaa!
[growls]
[GOKU]
Let's go!
Woo-hoo!
[SUPER BUU yells,
GOKU laughs]
[laughs]
[GOKU]
Look, Vegeta. People popcorn.
[VEGETA]
What is he on?
[OLD KAI giggles excitedly]
Ah, this is magnificent! They
actually escaped from Majin Buu!
--Yeah!
--[OLD KAI cackles]
Spectacular!
Fresh air and sunshine. Wow!
[VEGETA] That was a
disgusting experience.
[GOKU]
Aw. It wasn't that bad.
[VEGETA]
Speak for yourself.
[gasps]
They're back! And they
have everyone with them!
What a relief!
[VEGETA] Let's find a
safe place to drop these guys.
We still have some
unfinished business.
[GOKU]
Right.
Huh?!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Oh, boy. Here we go again.
[growls]
[SUPER BUU snarls]
[screams, grunts]
[VEGETA thinking]
How could he be increasing
instead of decreasing?!
[SUPER BUU yells]
If this keeps up,
he's going to be stronger
than he was before.
Yes. I know.
[SUPER BUU yells, rasps]
[yells]
Uh-oh. Look.
This is serious.
Told ya.
He's, uh, twice as
big as he was before.
Hey, look.
[shrieks]
[BOTH gasp]
[screaming continues]
[screams]
Watch. He's about to change.
[yells, growls]
[bellows]
[grunts]
Into a better dancer, I hope.
[KIBITO KAI]
Oh, no. He's changing back...
[whimpers]
Back... to normal.
Huh? Whatd'ya mean? "Normal"?
[pants]
[VEGETA laughs]
He's totally puny!
Dear me...
[KIBITO KAI]
I'm afraid we're doomed...
[OLD KAI] You said that he
was changing back to normal.
I don't get it!
I haven't seen this form yet.
How could it be normal?
Do you know something that
you haven't told me yet?
[KIBITO KAI]
Y-Yes, sir.
He shrunk. And you
were you so worried.
Hah! You weren't worried, huh?
You had white knuckles
and you know it.
[KIBITO KAI whimpers]
[NARRATOR] A dark cloud
has appeared in the sky.
But if Goku and
Vegeta aren't worried,
then why is Kibito Kai?
What does he know about
this little Buu that they don't?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z.