[NARRATOR]
Last time, on Dragon Ball Z!
[GOKU]
Hey, Buu!
I'd like you to
do me a little favor!
It's not like you to
break the rules, Kakarot!
I know! But I really
want to fight this guy
in the first round!
That way we'll both be
at one hundred percent
and it'll be a
totally fair match!
[NARRATOR]
With a little help from Buu,
Goku had his desire fulfilled!
And he was matched up
with the mystery fighter
in the first round
of the finals!
According to Goku,
the simple village boy
named Uub was, in fact,
a benevolent incarnation
of the evil Majin Buu!
[NARRATOR] But the boy wasn't
aware of his true powers,
and Goku wasn't beyond
using insult or injury
to coax them out!
[growls] My mom isn't fat!
My family's not ugly!
And my father's
not a bed wetter!
[NARRATOR]
And so the battle begins!
[yells]
[TRUNKS]
Huh?
[GOTEN]
Whoa!
[yells]
Huh?!
[ANNOUNCER]
Oh, my goodness!
It looks like Goku is out cold!
One! Two!
No! Wait! He's getting up!
This is really exciting!
There's no doubt about it!
That kid is Majin Buu all right!
[coughs]
[GOKU]
Hey! The fight's up here!
Huh?
Ha ha!
[UUB thinking]
I can't lose!
I promised everyone that
I'd return with the prize money!
I have to win!
Very good, but you
can do much better!
Whoa! Feel the power
of those blows!
They could stop
a train in its tracks!
Are you watching this?
I don't believe it!
The kid is actually learning how
to fight while he's fighting!
[GOKU]
Huh?
[KRILLIN] Are you guys
seeing what I'm seeing?
Oh, man unreal!
Yes! I see! He's great!
But that's your Dad!
Yeah! How can a boy
fight with Goku like that?
[BULMA]
This must be the guy!
The one that Goku
was talking about!
Is that possible?
Could a boy be that strong?
[VIDEL]
Huh?
This is great! What a fight!
Heck yeah!
[MR. SATAN yawns]
I think I'm gonna go take a nap.
A nap? You no watch fight?
Uh! Who cares!
Goku's going to win!
Then, he'll go to the finals
and face the great Majin Buu!
And after that, the
reigning champ, that'd be me,
is going to step in
and beat the winner
in the title fight!
I see!
Now what? How come when I...
What? What's this?
[Announcer] This is amazing!
Goku and Uub are perfectly
on par with one another!
Neither of them
is budging an inch!
[ANNOUNCER]
Wow!
That's four solid feet
of concrete giving way
under the sheer
magnitude of this fight!
Huh?! Oh, no! They'll
demolish the place!
[DENDE] Oh, he's giving
Goku a run for his money!
Mm! Indeed he is Dende.
And Goku must be loving it!
He's waited ten years for this!
Whoa! Now I've seen it all!
Goku is being swung
around by a boy half his size!
Your words are venom!
--[PAN] Grandpa!
--[MR. SATAN] No, no!
Please! Don't be hurt!
Goku!
No, he's gone!
Wow! Folks! This
could be a knock out!
Man! That little dude rocks!
Go get him!
[ANNOUNCER] Incredible! Goku
hardly has a scratch on him!
Pretty good try!
Ahhh! Let's go!
[cheering]
[gulps]
[KNOCK] What are these bad boys,
Captain? Some kind of mutants?
Well, I don't rightly know.
[KNOCK] I say we get the heck
out of here while we still can!
Yes?
[ATTENDENT] Hey, you two!
Wait a second!
[ATTENDENT] You guys are
finalists, aren't you?
My manager says you're not
supposed to leave the building!
Yeah! Well, I've
gotta go! Big number two!
Wait! What's this?
My Chicken Senses
are vibrating!
Yes! It's coming
in clear now!
There's a little
girl in distress!
B-Buck, bawk! Buck,
bawk! Buck, bawk!
Wings! Gizzard! Thigh!
The bad guy's gonna cry!
Captain Chicken away!
If he didn't want to fight, he
should have just said so! Geez!
[ANNOUNCER] Excellent! Young
Uub is still in the match!
[UUB thinking] I can't lose! I
gave them my word! All of them!
[UUB thinking] My family!
The elders! The children!
I promised them all!
Hmm?
I won't lose!
Whoa...
[MAN IN CROWD]
Wha...?!
Whoa! That's just not possible!
Ah! You can fly?
Ka... me...
...ha... me...
Dad! Don't do it!
Hello! I take it you don't
know quite how to fly yet, Uub.
Well, that's too bad!
It's only natural you know!
You need to find a Master
who can teach you these things!
I apologize for insulting
you earlier! Please forgive me!
Huh?
I just wanted to
see your true power.
It was all bottled up
inside until I made you mad!
But, hey! Look at you,
I think you learned
something about yourself!
You're strong! Real strong!
[GOKU] However,
you don't quite know how
to control your power yet.
I'll bet you've never fought
like this before, have you?
[UUB]
No! Not really!
Yeah! I see! Hmm?
Okay! Why not?
I've decided that from
now on I'm going to live
in your village and teach
you the art of fighting!
How does that sound?
You'll get a lot stronger!
Well? Whatd'ya say?
Why yes! Of course!
Oh, but...
Hmm? But what Uub?
[UUB]
See, I come from a poor family!
I spend my days
working with my father!
Sports are for fun, Goku!
But there's no time for that!
Oh, I see! Well, we'll just
have to find a sponsor for you!
Hey, I know! Perfect!
Mr. Satan has more money
than he does body hair, so...
He does?
Yeah! Don't worry!
You're covered!
But if anything
ever happens to me,
it'll be up to you to
maintain peace in the world!
Huh?
Be right back!
Huh?! 'Kay!
What's going on?
Hey guys, I hate to do this,
but i just wanted
to let you all know
I'm going to live in Uub's
village so I can train him!
--[CHICHI] Goku?
--[BULMA] That's lame!
I don't know how many
years this is gonna take,
but I promise
I'll visit you guys!
Thank you for understanding!
But we don't understand!
You're leaving for good?
Well! Sort of!
Sort of?
Not again!
You're leaving?
Gosh, Goku! It's kind
of sudden, isn't it?
[PAN]
Grandpa! It can't be true!
Tell me that it's
not true, Grandpa!
[sobs]
What's wrong? Hey!
Grandpa! Are you really leaving?
Yes! Hmm?
[PAN]
You can't go! It's not fair!
What am I going
to do without you?
[GOKU]
Hey! Hey! Pan! It's okay!
We'll still get to see
each other now and then!
Grandpa's going
to come and visit you!
Promise?
Yes! I promise.
I wouldn't miss it!
But you can't be sad
while I'm gone! Okay?
Okay! Sure!
Yeah! That's my girl!
[GOKU] Trunks, Goten, please
try to stay focused and train!
Look! I see a
bright future in Uub!
But you guys are the ones he's
gonna look to for leadership!
Right!
I'm gonna train too, Grandpa!
I'm gonna be big and strong like
you! And save the world, too!
[GOKU]
Yeah! That's the spirit!
[GOKU] Hey, Vegeta!
Sorry to disappoint you!
I was really looking
forward to one more bout
with the prince of all Saiyans!
Don't worry about it!
We couldn't play! Not here!
When we fight,
we'll need a whole
planet for an arena!
Ha, ha! You're too much!
Bye, my friend!
Well, let's boogie! Hop on!
Uhh! This okay?
Yeah, perfect! Now! You
live south of here, right?
Uh, huh!
Well, hold on! We're
heading south! 'Kay?
'Kay!
[GOKU]
Ready? And blast off!
Hey! Wait a sec!
Uub! Goku! Your match!
Aren't you going to finish?
[PAN] Goodbye, Grandpa!
Remember your promise!
[VIDEL] You mean your
Dad's gone! Just like that?
[GOHAN] Yeah, he has this
way of coming and going.
How could he?
I'm sorry!
But Goku's going to
have to grow up someday
and realize that there's
more to life than fighting!
He seemed happy to me.
More so than in a long time.
[DENDE]
Yeah! You're right, Piccolo!
Hmm? Uh, oh! He goes bye, bye?!
Yeah! He's leaving, Buu!
So! You're training
Uub to uphold the peace!
[VEGETA]
Is that it, Kakarot?
Well, you can't
fool me, old friend!
Yes! I know! There's more
to it than that, isn't there?
Hey! How 'bout it?
Huh? What?
After your training's finished
and you've become flawless,
how 'bout we fight again
so we can test our
powers on each other!
Yeah! Sure!
It'll be awesome!
To be honest, I can't
wait for that day to come!
It sounds thrilling?
Doesn't it?
Going head to head
in an all out battle!
Yeah!
All right!
[GOKU] Hold on tight,
Uub! Woohoo!
Uub! Let the training begin!
Yes!
No need be polite!
Yell! Let it go!
Yeah!!
Once more!
This time let
the whole world hear!
Yeah!
[GOKU, UUB laugh]
[NARRATOR]
Young Uub has been taken in
by the greatest Martial Arts
master in the Universe--
Goku, the orphan
who fell from the stars
to become the savior of mankind!
As the two set off
on a new adventure,
one thing is for certain--
as long as Goku lives, peace
and prosperity shall reign!