[VEGETA chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Having completed their
year-long journey to Earth,
the two sinister Saiyans
made their presence known
with explosive style!
The Earth's fighters
could only look on
in horror as the
destruction began,
for they had little hope
of defeating the Saiyans
without the help of their
greatest champion, Goku,
who was racing down Snake
Way to join the battle.
Unfortunately, the Saiyans
weren't willing to wait
for the hero's return.
They sought out their targets
with cruel precision,
hoping to learn the secrets
of the seven Dragon Balls.
Now Krillin, Piccolo, and
Gohan stand face to face
with these
Saiyan monsters,
and the diabolical henchmen
they've brought with them.
[SAIBAMEN growl]
[VEGETA] This should be
a pretty good match up.
These Saibamen
seem spunky.
[NARRATOR] Can our heroes
hold their ground long enough
for Goku's help
to arrive?
Find out, as the battle for
the Earth begins... Today!
[wind blows]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[SAIBAMEN growl]
Gohan! Pay attention!
Your thoughts are unfocused!
Uh, okay...
You don't have
to be scared!
Right!
[NAPPA snickers]
[SAIBAMEN yell]
[snarling]
[PICCOLO yells]
[KRILLIN yells]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[snarling]
[KRILLIN] Ahh!
Gohan, believe
in yourself.
[GOHAN]
I'll try...
[PICCOLO]
Don't try! Do it!
Right!
[NAPPA]
Aw, isn't that cute?
[VEGETA]
It warms my heart...
[KRILLIN] Don't listen
to those jerks, Gohan!
They'll get what's comin'
to 'em soon enough!
[CHIAOTZU]
Krillin!
[NAPPA grunts]
Hey, you guys!
[CHIAOTZU]
Hi, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Thanks
for dropping by!
[CHIAOTZU] Hm.
[KRILLIN] We could
use the help...
[TIEN] Looks like
the Saiyans brought
some of their friends
along for the ride...
No, they grew
them here...
[CHIAOTZU] What?
Don't ask...
That's okay. It doesn't
really matter...
Who's the kid? Is that
Goku's little boy?
[KRILLIN] Uh-huh.
His name is Gohan.
Piccolo's been
training him.
Hm. He's bold,
like his father.
[CHIAOTZU] Ah!
[NAPPA] Enough of this
garbage! Saibamen!
I want to hear
them beg for mercy!
[SAIBAMEN grunt and growl]
[YAMCHA]
Wait for me!
[VEGETA] Hm?
What's up?
Sorry I'm late!
H-Hey! Yamcha!
So, why is everyone acting
all serious around here?
[KRILLIN and CHIAOTZU laugh]
[VEGETA] Look, Nappa,
now it's six against six.
Their warriors
against our Saibamen!
How perfect.
This may just prove to be
interesting after all...
Heh, heh, heh. I can't wait.
[VEGETA] Gentlemen!
How would you like to
make a match of this
and fight our
soldiers one by one?
Well? Answer.
[growling]
We're not here
to play games!
And we're not going to
fight on your terms!
We'll take you
all on at once!
Hey, now... Easy!
We're still waiting
for Goku to show up!
We can buy ourselves some time
by playing it their way.
I'll go first! I'm not afraid
of these little creeps.
It'll be a
good warm-up!
[NAPPA] Ha, ha, ha, ha!
That's the spirit!
Fresh meat for
the grinder!
But just wait...
You won't be so
cocky when you see
what these 'little
creeps' can do!
[SAIBAMEN cackling]
Well! A lot of noise,
but no volunteers!
All right, you go. But don't
hold anything back... Got it?
[SAIBAMAN 1 grunts]
Hey, Tien!
Be careful!
[KRILLIN] Hm?
[helicopter blades whir]
Don't get too close...
That big bald one is loaded!
[TECH MAN] Gotcha!
We're just gonna ease forward
until we can get a
good shot of the aliens!
[TV REPORTER] That's it.
There they are! Back a little...
Hey Mike!
We got it!
Can you zoom
in any more?
[NAPPA]
Heh, hah, heh, heh, heh...
So you want some news, do ya?
[NAPPA grunts]
[NAPPA] Here!
Now you are the news!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[NAPPA] Good!
No more distractions!
Now whadda ya' say we
get this fight started!
[SAIBAMAN 1 grunts]
[VEGETA chuckles]
--[REPORTERS] Mister Yajirobe!
--[YAJIROBE] You there!
[TV REPORTER 2] Mister Yajirobe!
If you are a member
of the special forces,
why aren't you
there with them now?
Because!
I'm hungry! That's why!
[CONCERNED MOTHER]
What horrible manners!
Look! It's a strategy!
The other guys are wearin'
'em down in the first round,
and I'm saving my
energy for round two!
[TV REPORTER 3] And who are
the other members of your team?
You've probably
heard of them...
You might've even
seen them in action
in the Worlds Martial
Arts Tournament.
First, there's Goku. Then
there's Yamcha and Krillin...
You know Goku?
Know him?
I'm his trainer!
[REPORTERS murmur]
Yeah, Goku's definitely
our best man.
That is, if he makes
it back in time...
[TV REPORTER 4]
Where is Goku now?
[BULMA]
Ugh! I can't believe this!
[REPORTERS chatter on TV]
[OX KING]
Hey, gang!
[ALL] Ox King!
[ROSHI]
Hey there, Ox...
Thank goodness you didn't
bring ChiChi with you.
That was a good move!
Oh, well, uh...
Please... What's happened
to Gohan? Where is he?
[ROSHI] Umm...
Master Roshi! You have to tell
me! I can handle it! Please!
He's on the battlefield
with Piccolo.
[CHICHI gasps]
[OX KING] ChiChi!
[SAIBAMAN 1 growls]
[GOHAN gulps]
[snarling]
[TIEN yells]
[SAIBAMAN 1 cackles]
Wow. Thanks.
[TIEN yells]
What?
Impossible!
[SAIBAMAN 1 groans]
--[KRILLIN laughs]
--[CHIAOTZU] Yay!
Way to go, Tien!
Great move!
[GOHAN laughs]
Alright! Heh!
[CHIAOTZU]
You're the best, Tien!
[TIEN]
Thanks.
[VEGETA] It looks like you got
a hold of a weak batch, Nappa.
No! They're all good!
These are the same
ones that survived
that crazy
battle on Tratak!
He should have won!
His power level's 1200!
All of these Saibamen have
the same fighting power as...
[VEGETA]
As who?
As Raditz.
Now do you
see my point?
Well, I think so.
[VEGETA chuckles]
Do you?
Well, don't
strain yourself,
just leave the thinking
to me from now on.
[SAIBAMAN 1 groans]
Uh, Tien? That one's
getting back up!
[TIEN] Huh?
[SAIBAMAN 1 groans]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[NAPPA]
Vegeta! Why?
[VEGETA] He wasn't of
any use to us any more.
I know, but...
he was... alive!
[VEGETA] Hmph.
[gasps]
[GOHAN whimpers]
I-I don't understand...
[VEGETA] It would
have been pointless
to let him continue,
Nappa. He was losing.
Which leads me to believe
he wasn't trying his hardest.
I specifically told him
not to hold anything back.
Whoa... Talk
about ruthless!
[thinking] No mercy.
Even for his allies...
He won't be taking prisoners.
We're fighting for our lives.
This is just crazy! I've never
seen anything like it!
[PRODUCER] Remote One,
report to control!
[TECH 1] Wow! There's enough
energy bouncing around out there
to light up
a whole city!
[TECH 2] Mike, we're having
trouble holding a signal here!
[DIRECTOR] Yeah, I copy that.
Just do the best you can!
[electrical strikes]
So... Who's going next?
[GOHAN whimpers and gulps]
All right! If no one steps up,
we'll have a free for all!
[PICCOLO] That's fine
with me! Let's do it!
No! I'll go next!
[YAMCHA]
Hold on, Krillin!
What's up?
Let me go,
would ya?
I'm really anxious
to show these guys
what we're all about
down here on this planet.
That's great, but,
I got this one, okay?
[YAMCHA] You've already
been wished back
with the Dragon Balls
once. I haven't.
So if anything happens,
at least we know that
I can be revived...
Sit this one out
for me, Krillin...
You'll get your chance,
don't you worry about that.
'Kay... He's all yours.
Heh, heh, heh...
How touching. I'm all
warm and tingly. Heh!
Now go kill him!
[SAIBAMAN 2 grunts]
Alright then... C'mon!
Let's get this thing over with!
Huh... This one
seems eager.
Yeah, right...
[NAPPA]
Eager to die, that is...
[SAIBAMAN 2 growls]
[ANCHOR MAN] It seems one
of the little green men
is about to take
on another member
of the Special
Forces team.
The leader of this elite
task force, Mr. Yajirobe,
will be available
for comment...
[OOLONG]
Oh, brother...
[ANCHOR MAN]
After eating.
[BULMA] Ew, look how
ugly those things are!
[PUAR] No kidding!
[ANCHOR MAN] It looks
like the Special Forces
are ready for action!
Yamcha!
Isn't he great? I've never
seen him look so confident!
It's not just appearance!
He's reached a new level!
Excuse me!
Hey, Bulma...
Something caught your eye?
Huh? What do
you mean?
Oh, don't mind
him, Bulma!
I think
it's wonderful
that you're still
in love with Yamcha!
Oh, well, I guess
it's pretty obvious.
[ROSHI]
Ahh! What was that for?
[OOLONG] Hey, look!
There's Piccolo!
[OX KING and TURTLE] Huh?
[OOLONG] Boy, he doesn't
look too happy, does he?
[ROSHI] Oh, wow, Ox!
Look who it is!
Huh? Gohan's huge!
[CHICHI gasps]
[CHICHI]
Where's Gohan?
[CHICHI] Oh, my goodness!
What happened to him?
Nothing! He's just bigger
and stronger, that's all!
Oh, Gohan... You've been
growing up without me...
[BULMA] He looks like
Goku when he was a boy!
[CHICHI] Aahh!
Don't tell me
my little boy
is going to have to
fight those monsters!
[CHICHI whimpers]
[OX KING] ChiChi!
[ROSHI] If only
Goku were here...
[SAIBAMAN 2 snarls]
They... vanished!
Nonsense! They're just
moving very fast!
Try to feel out
their energies...
Feel their
energies?
[PICCOLO] All of us are
watching them right now,
except you, Gohan!
What? You can see
them? 'Kay...
[PICCOLO] Don't focus
on a specific point.
Let your eyes take in your
entire surroundings...
Remember, you're not
trying to see their bodies
but the light that the energy
in their bodies gives off.
[whooshing sounds]
[GOHAN] Uh! I can
hear them, Piccolo!
[PICCOLO] Good...
Now stay relaxed.
Continue to look...
Don't blink your eyes.
[whooshing sounds continue]
Ah!
Now you see.
[whooshing sounds continue]
[YAMCHA and SAIBAMAN 2
yell frantically]
[grunts and yells]
[YAMCHA] Aahh!
[YAMCHA yells]
[YAMCHA]
Oh, no you don't!
[SAIBAMAN 2] Yah!
[YAMCHA chuckles]
[YAMCHA grunts and yells]
[SAIBAMAN 2 yells]
--[KRILLIN] Alright!
--[CHIAOTZU] Yay!
Wow... Great.
[BULMA, OOLONG, PUAR,
and ROSHI laugh and cheer]
[BULMA]
Yay! He did it! Way to go!
That's two!
Well...
That was easy.
Looks like we're in a
different league altogether
than your little
green goon squad!
You cocky...
Nappa! Relax.
Now then, whadda you
say I just take on
the other four
by myself?
[KRILLIN] Yamcha!
Are you nuts?
[VEGETA] Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Now that, I'd like to see.
Too bad I won't
get the chance...
[YAMCHA] Oh yeah?
Bring 'em on!
[GOHAN gasps]
[gasps]
Let go!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[grunting continues]
[SAIBAMAN 2 snarls]
It's over...
Ah! Oh no...
[SAIBAMAN 2 yells]
[yelling]
Yamcha...
Well... I guess
it's a draw.
Kamikaze...
No way to defend...
Ah! Is he...
[KRILLIN quavering]
No... He's dead...
[VEGETA laughs]
Hey, what happened,
you guys?
It looked like he...
was going to win...
I don't exactley know, Bulma...
But it doesn't look good.
[ROSHI] I'm sorry, everyone...
I'm afraid we've lost him.
[PUAR gasps and sobs]
No! Yamcha!
Please! Don't go!
No, no, no, no!
[PUAR cries]
[BULMA whimpers]
[PUAR cries and BULMA whimpers]
[ROSHI] Bulma, it's
okay to let it out...
But...
[BULMA sobs]
Oh, Master Roshi!
[ROSHI] That's it.
Let it all out.
Everything's going
to be all right.
[BULMA] But why did it
have to be Yamcha? Why?
Now why'd you have to
go and be the hero,
you big,
stupid, jerk...
It was my
turn to fight.
It shoulda' been
me in there...
You hear me, Yamcha?
You can't die!
It should've been me!
It should have been me!
Oh, shut up! It doesn't
make any difference
who goes
down first!
Don't you get it? You're
all going to die in the end!
[VEGETA]
Calm down, Nappa.
Give them a moment to clear
this trash off the battlefield.
How dare you!
You guys stay
out of this!
This is between
me and them now!
'Kay buddy...
This one's for you.
I won't let you
down again...
All right, come
on! I'm ready!
[KRILLIN] I'll take on all
four of those goons at once!
[KRILLIN] Just like
Yamcha was going to do!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[NARRATOR] The demented Saibamen
have claimed their first victim
on the battlefield...
Now, fueled by rage,
Krillin intends to ensure
they do not claim a second.
Can Krillin avenge
his fallen friend,
and put an end to the
Saiyans' twisted game?
Don't miss the action
when Krillin strikes!
Next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!