[NARRATOR]
It was bomb's away
on the last episode
of Dragon Ball Z,
as Goku launched
the Spirit Bomb
with the full
force of his being.
[GOKU] Maybe you'll
come back some day.
As... As a better person,
I hope. I'd like that.
Perhaps we'll have
a little one-on-one!
[NARRATOR] It was time to say
goodbye and send Buu packing!
[GOKU]
Adios!
I'll be waiting
for you, Majin Buu!
--[DENDE] Goku!
--Kakarot!
--Father!
--Goku!
Do it!
[NARRATOR]
There was nothing left to do
except to beat the Buu!
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] And with a
resounding flourish of power,
Goku wrote the final
words in the chapter
and closed the book
on his old nemesis
once and for all!
[KID BUU screams]
[NARRATOR]
At last, the war was over.
Nothing remained of Majin Buu
except the battle scars
that he left behind.
The Universe was
safe once again.
[KIBITO KAI]
He really did it! Outstanding!
[KIBITO KAI laughs]
Of course Goku could do it!
[laughs]
[ALL laugh, cheer]
[KING YEMMA] I knew it!
I knew it! Yah, ha, ha!
He can not be defeated!
[PICCOLO]
So, what do you think?
Are you feeling
what I'm feeling?
[GOHAN]
I think so.
The fight's over.
[GOHAN] But is it over for good?
Or is he going to regenerate?
No, there's not a
trace of him left.
I think he's really
gone this time, you guys.
We won!
[BOTH laugh]
Ahh... Dad!
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Well, is he... i-is he gone?
Did you finish him off?
Ahh! Tell me!
You did!
[laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
Didn't you?
[laughs]
We did it! It's over!
Citizens of the Earth,
this is the Champ speaking!
Majin Buu has been destroyed!
He is no more!
And the nightmare is over!
[gasping]
[MR. SATAN]
Thanks to your help,
we can all live in
peace once again!
[cheering]
Hallelujah, Champ! Wow!
Hooh! You're the man!
My gosh! He really
did it! He's amazing!
Yyyyeeess!
All right, Champ!
[ALL] Satan! Satan!
Satan! Satan!
[chanting continues]
[groans]
Oh! How embarrassing!
--Goku and Vegeta rock!
--[ALL cheering]
[cheering continues]
[BULMA]
I love you, Vegeta!
[laughter]
[BEE barks]
Hey! Look at the
mighty puppy dog!
[laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
That tickles! Ha, ha, ha!
[DENDE]
Goku! You did it!
[DENDE laughs]
Well! It's not too bad
considering what went on here.
At least the grass is short.
I got ant bites
from that other planet.
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU] Hmm? Oh! Dende. You'd
better get to Vegeta first.
He really got the
tar beat out of him.
Right.
[DENDE]
Just relax, Vegeta.
There. That oughta do it.
[VEGETA sighs]
What a day! Are you
as hungry as I am, boy?
[barks]
[MR. SATAN]
Hmm? What's wrong?
Hey! Where are you going?
Thanks, Dende!
[DENDE laughs]
[BEE whines]
[gasps]
I-It's Buu!
Huh?! What?!
[BEE whines]
[MR. SATAN]
Buu! Are you okay?!
Buu! You're alive!
Hey, little green guy,
come here! Quick!
Use your powers on him
before he dies! Please!
[VEGETA]
What are you talking about?!
Have you lost your mind?! Move!
Get back! It's not
over until he is dead!
But he's different than he was!
He would never do those
bad things ever again!
You saw him!
He faught that evil
Buu with all he had!
[VEGETA] All right,
and what if he's not all gone?
What if he blows his stack again
and produces another
killing machine? What then?!
Well, I don't know.
[VEGETA] Well, I do! It would
mean the end of the world!
You might be willing to
take that gamble, but I'm not!
[MR. SATAN] But h-he
wouldn't have blown his stack
if that idiot hadn't shot
his puppy with a rifle!
Please! I beg you!
I'll take full responsibility.
He can live with me!
Oh sure, that sounds great!
Until his little mut is run over
in the street some day!
Clear out, fool! Or you'll die
with your friend!
[MR. SATAN sobs]
[whimpers]
Darn! Idiot!
[GOKU] Dende, go ahead
and heal him, okay?
[gasping]
Are you nuts?
Explain! Right now!
I'm just returning
the favor, that's all.
Remember what happened when
Majin Buu had you pinned down?
The big Buu attacked
and got him off of you.
And then yelled for Hercule
to carry you off to safety.
[MR. SATAN]
I've got you...
Hey, you! What're
you waiting for?
Right?
[GOKU] The fact is, Vegeta,
if it wasn't for these two,
the Earth would
be gone right now.
I think that gives them
as much right to live here
as anyone else!
And you know it.
Yes, but, the Earthlings
don't know what went on up here.
I think that their fear of Buu
is going to cause
some serious problems.
Yeah, I see what you mean.
Let's see...
I guess we could keep Buu
indoors and away from everyone
for the first six months.
Then we could
use the Dragon Balls
to wish the Earthlings'
memory of Buu away.
See? It's that simple.
Yeah, sure! Just
wish it away! Great!
Well, then. It's
all settled, right?
[VEGETA] Yes, that'sa brilliant
idea! If you don't have a brain.
Thank you so much!
I'll never forget this!
Good! It's unanimous!
Right!
[GOKU] I don't know about
you guys, but I'm starving!
I say after Dende's finished, we
head home and get a bite to eat!
[BEE barks]
[NARRATOR] And so the
four warriors took wing
and returned to Earth
after a job well done.
--Thanks for everything!
--So long!
--Hey!
--[DENDE laughs]
--[BULMA gasps]
--Yes!
[OX-KING]
He-He-Hey!
[laughing]
--[MR. POPO] Dende! Oh!
--[DENDE] Oh, Popo!
[GOTEN]
Daddy! You did it!
Hey!
[VEGETA]
Yes, son?
[GOTEN]
Show me the Spirit Bomb, Dad!
[GOKU]
Not now, Son!
[VIDEL laughs]
--[VIDEL] Hi, Daddy!
--[MR. SATAN gasps]
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[BEE barks]
Oh! Look!
[screaming]
--[TRUNKS growls]
--[GOKU] Easy there, Trunks!
Whoa! Whoa-ho-ho!
[VEGETA] It's okay, Son!
He's our... guest...
[BUU giggles]
[chuckles]
[GOKU]
It sure is nice to be back!
Sorry I've been gone so long!
But guess what?
Old Kai granted me a life
so I'm not dead anymore!
You're kidding me?!
You mean we're
going to live together?
As a family of four
in our little house?!
Well, that's what
I was planning on
if you guys think
you can put up with me!
[CHICHI gasps]
[sobbing]
[GOKU]
There, there, ChiChi. It's okay.
--[CHICHI] I know! I know!
--[ROSHI] Aww...
--[CHICHI sobs]
--[GOKU] Gosh, ChiChi!
Did you cry this
much when I died?
But don't worry,
I'm back for good. I love you.
[PEOPLE gasping, screaming]
[NARRATOR] True to his word,
in six months time,
Goku summoned the Dragon
and wished that Majin Buu
be erased from
the peoples' memory.
[GOKU] Thanks, Shenron!
It's great to see you again!
[MAJIN BUU hums]
[indistinct chatter]
[SALESMAN] Hot pretzels!
Get your hot pretzels here!
Y'want salt? No salt?
Doesn't matter.
[BUU]
Hmm...
[GIRL] Go away! This is
my cone! Go get your own!
[BUU]
Buu's own cone? Where get cone?
Right over there, bud!
At the cone shop!
Oh, my! Lookee, lookee! Wow!
Fourteen flavors!
Two for every day of the week!
So, like, which flavor
would you like today, sir?
Buu want... all! All cones!
[gasps]
[CLERK] That's all
14 flavors, Sir!
[BUU laughs]
Hey! Wait a second!
Like, you haven't paid!
[BUU]
Hmm? Buu has his cone!
Yes, dude, but it's not free!
You have to give me
money for that! Now here!
Huh? Ohh! That's mine!
Give it back!
Forget it, buddy! Money first!
[growls]
--[gasps]
--[CASHIER screams]
[BUU growls]
Never, ever, Buu! Do you
hear me! Don't get angry!
Sorry! Buu not
supposed to get angry.
Whoa! That was weird!
Buu needs money for ice cream!
Buu want ice cream
but Buu needs money
for ice cream,
so Buu want money!
[PEOPLE gasping]
[BOOKIE] Look at all this
money in my hand, people!
[BUU]
Money?
[BOOKIE]
It can all be yours
if you manage to stay on
your feet for three minutes
against my associate,
Pit Bull Pete!
Listen up, gentlemen.
It only costs 10,000
zennies to try!
But you get 100,000
zennies if you win!
So come on, guys!
Prove your manhood
to your sweetheart
and get rich at the same time!
Three minutes, fellas!
What have you got to lose?
Are ya gonna try it?
Are you crazy! That guy's
a professional! It's a scam!
You try! You're
pretty tough! Huh?
[BUU] If Buu wins,
he can have man's money?
That's right!
You just have to stay on your
feet for three short minutes.
It'll be a fair fight!
Fight? Mister Satan
told Buu never to fight!
Did you hear that? He must be
Mr. Satan's pupil!
Wow! That would
make for a good match!
It's not a fight!
It's a game! That's all, pal!
Oh! Great! Buu play!
Right on! I'll cover
the challenger!
It'll be worth it just to see
the Champ's pupil in action!
Here!
[chuckles]
[PIT BULL BILL thinking]
You're goin' down, bubble butt!
Big time!
Money! Ice cream!
Ready! Go!
[PIT BULL PETE grunting]
Ha, ha, ha! So this is the pupil
of the great Mr. Satan, huh?!
Money! Ice cream!
[PIT BULL PETE] You pink whale!
That's from Pit Bull Pete!
Ice cream! Money! Ice cream!
[PIT BULL PETE grunts]
Ohhhh!
Peter! Aaaahh! Are you okay?!
Speak to me, big guy! Please!
Ice cream!
[WOMAN]
Look! There he is!
That's the guy who
knocked out Pit Bull Pete!
[BUU hums]
[MAN]
You've got to be kidding me!
[CASHIER] Oh, my gosh! That's a
hundred thousand zennies!
Wait! Pink dude! Your change!
Sir! You gave me too much money!
What? You keep money!
Buu keep ice cream!
Thank you! Enjoy your cones!
[BULMA growls]
Men! I swear! You can't
trust them, can you?
Carry that bag for me,
would you, Buu?
If Vegeta and Trunks think
they can just fly off every time
the shopping takes
more than an hour,
they've got
another thing coming!
[BULMA]
Hello? Earth to Buu?!
Majin Buu!
[PIT BULL PETE]
That's it, over there!
[SALESMAN] They'd all look
lovely on you, Ma'am!
But if I had to pick,
I'd go with this!
For sure! It's
elegant, yet bold.
Fine! That one!
And the rest as well!
Uhh, Ma'am? You
mean the entire case?
Yep! That's right!
Rock Candy is Buu's favorite!
You don't eat diamonds!
[PIT BULL PETE growls]
Freeze! This is a hold up!
[CUSTOMER]
They've got guns!
[screaming]
[whimpers]
Listen, Buster! Nobody tells me
what to do! Understand?!
--Shut up! Dumb broad!
--[BOOKIE] Aaah! Look! The cops!
[sirens wailing]
[BOOKIE]
I don't wanna go to jail!
Be quiet! We're in control!
We've got hostages!
Keep your cool, fool!
I don't know! One of your
hostages here is Majin Buu!
You have a lot
to be nervous about!
Majin who? A tough guy, huh?
Well, I ain't scared of him!
I've beat up more men
than ten gangs combined!
Not good!
Well, where is he?!
Come out, dude!
If you don't, I'm gonna-
Pete! It's that guy
from the street! Look!
Shut up! What guy?!
That guy!
[PIT BULL PETE screams]
Hey! You nice man!
Give Buu money for ice cream!
Stay away! Back! Back!
[CUSTOMERS shout, scream]
You dropped this!
Oh! That was a gunshot!
We're gonna have to move in!
[SAIYAMAN]
Officer! Wait!
Oh! Wow! Saiyaman!
We shall take it
from here, officer!
Certainly!
Now! Evil must cower!
And the righteous
must flourish!
So says Saiyaman!
And Saiyagirl!
[BOTH]
Protectors of truth and justice!
[POLICE CHIEF]
Ah! They're just coming out.
Huh. Well. [chuckles]
[PIT BULL PETE]
Please! Take us in! We give up!
[GOHAN, VIDEL groan]
[BULMA giggles]
[BOTH laugh]
[GOTEN, TRUNKS laugh]
[GOTEN]
This is fun!
[laughter continues]
[GOKU laughs]
[GOTEN, TRUNKS grunting]
[GOTEN]
Hey! That's not fair!
Things are finally
back to normal.
[GOTEN]
Now you're gonna get it, Dad!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fuuuusion... Haaa!
[GOKU yells]
Hmm, hmm, hmm! There!
Now it's our turn!
--Geronimo!
--[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] Ow! So you
wanna play rough, huh?!
[GOTENKS]
Uh-oh! Hit the deck!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
If I were you guys,
I'd stay fused together so
ChiChi can only spank you once!
[GOKU laughs]
[laughter]
[CHICHI] Goten! Trunks!
What do you think you're doing?!
Get your clothes
on this instant!
[GOTENKS]
Aaah!
[CHICH] Don't you dare run
from me! You get back here!
[NARRATOR]
At last, peace has returned
and everyone was
having a good time.
Well, almost...
[VEGETA]
What are you looking at?