[NARRATOR] On the last episode
of Dragon Ball Z,
the battle to decide the fate
of the Universe continued,
as Super Saiyan 3 Goku
went head to head
with the elastic Majin Buu.
--[KID BUU grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
[GOKU]
Ka... Me...
[KID BUU screams]
[NARRATOR]
Goku fought valiantly,
but the more brilliant
the attack,
the more demoralizing the result
against the seemingly
invincible Buu.
[NARRATOR]
It was an impossible situation
of nightmarish proportions,
one made to order for
the unshakeable Saiyan.
[NARRATOR] And after Vegeta
had tried and failed
to measure up to the same test,
the proud Saiyan prince
finally realized
that Goku was truly
in a league of his own.
[VEGETA thinking]
You're better than me, Kakarot.
You are the best.
--[GOKU groaning]
--[KID BUU grunting]
[NARRATOR]
The battle rages on today.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[screams]
[MR. SATAN groaning]
It's getting worse!
This is the mother
of all nightmares, Bee!
--[MR. SATAN groans]
--[BEE gasps]
[MR. SATAN]
Hold on, boy!
[laughing]
[GOKU]
Ka.... Me...
Ha... Me...
Ha!
[KID BUU screams]
[GOKU pants]
Huh. You can't deflect that one.
No way!
[GOKU] This is crazy.
I'm going nowhere fast.
[VEGETA thinking]
Hang in there, Kakarot.
[GOKU grunts, yells]
--[KID BUU grunts]
--[GOKU yelling]
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH groan]
[GOKU gasps]
[KID BUU groans]
[GOKU yells]
--[GOKU yells]
--[KID BUU groans]
[KID BUU laughs]
[GOKU yells]
[KID BUU]
Huh?
[GOKU grunts]
--[GOKU grunting]
--[KID BUU groans]
[GOKU yells]
[KABITO KAI]
No, our beautiful planet.
He blasted straight through.
Enough, get a grip!
The entire Universe
is at stake here!
Let him trash our planet
if he wants to.
We might be homeless,
but we'll still be Kais.
[KABITO KAI]
Yes, sir.
Come on, Goku. You're the one.
[panting]
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU]
Ah!
[GOKU screams]
[KID BUU laughs]
[groans]
You're really strong.
Stronger than I imagined.
[chuckles]
Me Buu, kill you!
[GOKU]
Is that so?
Well, you wouldn't be the first.
And there's always that chance.
But, what I represent can
never be destroyed, Majin Buu!
[KID BUU laughs]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU groans]
[panting]
[KID BUU whistles]
Shoot! My attacks aren't having
any effect on him anymore.
--[GOKU] What's going on?
--[KID BUU whistles]
[KID BUU laughs]
[KRILLIN]
Aw, man! That hurts.
[YAMCHA] What happened?
Did he attack Goku?
[KRILLIN] No, worse.
He's making fun of him.
Goku's attacks aren't working.
[KID BUU yells]
[GOKU grunts, yells]
[GOKU] Man, I feel like
a hamster on a wheel.
It doesn't matter how
much energy I put out,
I still don't get anywhere.
[VEGETA]
Kakarot.
Hm? Hey, we'll switch
in a little while okay?
I still have some
fight left in me.
Ha. I know you don't intend
to switch, you can't fool me.
Come on, you know
better than anyone
that I don't stand a chance
against Buu at this level.
He'd tear me apart!
What? No! You'd do fine.
Mm. Don't give me that!
I know what you're
trying to do, Kakarot.
So forget it. I fought him.
I had my chance.
I know the truth.
He's stronger than me,
you know that.
Vegeta.
Go get him.
Don't you worry about me.
You're a Super Saiyan 3!
You should be able to generate
more than enough power
to destroy that monster!
[GOKU] Well, maybe I could have
done it when I was fresh,
but I let the fight drag
on so you could have a shot.
Huh?!
I should have done it! Darn it!
Now I'm weak! I'll need time.
How much time?
If I even had one minute.
Just one minute
with no interruptions.
In this fight,
one minute is eternity.
[GOKU]
Oh, man! I don't believe this.
He's having the time of
his life over there.
Buu yeah! Buu yeah! Buu yeah!
[GOKU growls]
He's just playing games.
[VEGETA]
Kakarot, I've got it covered.
[gasps]
Your minute,
I've got it covered.
Get the rest that you need.
But, Vegeta. You could die.
If I can't last one lousy minute
then perhaps I deserve to die.
Hey, that's not true.
[VEGETA]
Sixty seconds, Kakarot!
[KID BUU laughing, taunting]
[VEGETA] All right, I'm going.
You have one minute.
Forget it. No way!
You've already tried fighting
him once. You could be killed!
[VEGETA] Tell me, is there
any other way, Kakarot?
[VEGETA]
Do you want to beat him, or not?
Yes, I do.
[VEGETA] Then what do you say we
drop this idiotic sentiment
and win this thing.
And don't worry about me,
I'll keep my end of the deal.
Hm. Why not? I'll do it.
All right, but on one condition.
I don't want you
to do anything reckless.
Just hold him off
and that's it, okay?
You don't have to win this.
So don't get angry
and blow yourself up again.
You died once.
If anything happens to you now,
you won't exist anymore.
There'll be nothing I can do
to bring you back.
Stay alive. Okay?
Thanks, but I'm already dead.
Well, here goes.
[VEGETA grunts, pants]
[VEGETA yells]
[GOKU yells]
[KID BUU laughing, taunting]
[yells]
Not again! Can't they fight
the old fashioned way?
Please! Somebody wake me up!
[VEGETA grunting]
Not bad. Now, if he can
keep that up for a minute,
we should do just fine.
[VEGETA grunting]
[KID BUU laughs]
[gasps, groans]
[VEGETA screams]
[VEGETA groaning]
[KID BUU laughs]
[GOKU thinking]
Vegeta...
[KRILLIN] He's down.
Vegeta's down. This is awful!
[VEGETA gasping]
Just a little longer.
[KID BUU chuckles]
[VEGETA] You're going to wish
you hadn't done that.
Come on!
[VEGETA grunts]
[KID BUU laughs]
[VEGETA]
What are you laughing at?
[yells]
--[VEGETA grunts]
--[KID BUU groans]
[yells]
[laughs]
[VEGETA groans]
[GOKU]
This is not good.
Oh no.
[DENDE]
Vegeta!
--[KABITO KAI gasping]
--[OLD KAI sighs]
[GOKU]
Uh, oh. I'm not ready yet!
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA]
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Vegeta!
[VEGETA groaning]
What's wrong? Leaving? So soon?
[VEGETA]
You're no warrior!
You're just a mindless
freak of nature.
A big wad of spit out
chewing gum.
Is this what you want?
Well, is it?
I don't think so.
You're scared, aren't you?
Go ahead and run away!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[KID BUU growling]
That's it, yes.
Huh?!
Take this, fool!
Blast!
[VEGETA groans]
--[KID BUU grunting]
--[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGETA gasps]
Come on, please. Almost there.
Just a little bit longer.
--[KID BUU grunts. chuckles]
--[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA screams]
[KID BUU laughing]
[VEGETA]
What's so funny, freak?
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
What are you gawking at?
What did you think, huh?
[VEGETA] That I was gonna
roll over and die
from an attack like that?
[growls]
You're nothing,
just a trickster.
I am a warrior!
The Saiyan Prince!
Vegeta!
[KRILLIN] Vegeta has no reserves
left. He's in serious trouble.
Darn! Why's Goku taking so long?
It's been more than a minute.
[GOKU] I don't get it.
I should have been done by now.
Why isn't this working?
I need more time!
It's not enough!
[KID BUU]
Huh?!
[KID BUU, VEGETA grunting]
--[VEGETA yelling]
--[KID BUU laughing]
--[VEGETA groans]
--[KID BUU grunts]
Ah!
[VEGETA screams, gasps]
Ah! Ah. Ha, ha, ha, ha.
[choking]
[GOKU grunts]
Vegeta, no.
I can't take this.
It's too much to bear.
[NARRATOR] As Goku struggles
to amass the power he needs,
Vegeta is being throttled
by the long arm of Majin Buu.
And the villain is finding
a sadistic pleasure
in squeezing the life
from the Saiyan prince.
How long can Vegeta withstand
the deadly assault,
and how long can
Goku stand to watch?
Stay tuned to find out!