[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the race to
save Earth continued!
Kami and Mr. Popo
smashed their way through
the Guardian's Graveyard
with Earth's last chance;
the Sacred Water.
But before Kami could
pour the Sacred Water
into the air currents,
the former guardians of Earth
showed up to claim his spirit.
That's bad news for Piccolo,
because every minute
Kami stays below his Lookout,
Piccolo's strength
fades a little more.
You lose!
[grunts]
[NARRATOR] Luckily, Gohan's
not ready to give up yet!
But how long can he
keep a gargantuan of girth
like Garlic Jr.
from falling on Piccolo?
It's going to take a lot
more than fancy footwork,
on today's episode
of Dragon Ball Z!
[distant rumbling]
[commotion]
[yells]
[chuckles]
[GOHAN yells]
What?
[grunts]
Piccolo? What's wrong?
Your arm! It's disappeared!
Heh, it's Kami. He's the
reason I'm fading away.
[MALE VOICE] I can see you're
tired. Wouldn't you like to
put your feet up
and rest for eternity?
No! Kami, stay back!
[MALE VOICE] Have it your way!
[yells]
Leave him alone!
[KAMI groans, yells]
[POPO hollers]
[yells]
[KAMI groans]
Please! Speak to me!
[KAMI laughs]
[MALE VOICE]
Kami, if you have a good joke,
why don't you share it?
I just find it hard
to believe that you were
once a guardian
of Earth like me!
[KAMI] Look what has
become of you! All of you!
You're nothing but
a bunch of bullies!
Just bullies, I say!
[laughing]
[MALE VOICE] Don't forget,
Kami, you're in our world now!
For now I am! But I don't
plan on staying here very long!
The earth needs me!
Time is running out!
Please get out of my way!
[MALE VOICE] Why are you
so eager to leave this place?
I must!
Because if I don't, the earth
will suffer a horrible fate!
[KAMI] As the current
guardian of Earth,
it is my responsibility
to look after
all things on the planet.
And I will do that even if
it means sacrificing myself!
It's my job!
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have work to do!
I've had it with you...
It's over!
Huh?
[bellows]
[GARLICE JR. yells]
[groans]
[yells]
Great shot! A hole in one!
[laughs]
Gohan! It's still not over!
Right!
[yells]
[chuckles]
Thanks a lot! I needed to
lose a couple of pounds!
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
That's impossible!
[chuckles]
You pack a big punch
for such a little kid!
But I think your plan of attack
has a few holes in it!
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
He's alive? But Gohan
plowed right through him!
That doesn't matter.
He used the Dragon Balls
to make himself
immortal, remember?
Huh?
[yells, grunts]
How'd, he do that?
Now it's my turn to
have a little fun!
[GARLIC JR. yells]
Piccolo!
[yells, groans]
[yells]
Huh?
[KAMI yells]
[yells]
[chuckles]
Piccolo.
[PICCOLO groans]
[yells]
[GARLIC JR.] Hm!
Like they say, "An old
Namekian never dies...
he just fades away!"
[laughs]
[yells]
That hurt!
[GOHAN] Aah!
He shoots! He scores!
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
Can't... give... up!
I'll be ready
to fight as soon as
I get some feeling
back in my legs.
Then I'll show him who's boss!
Ha! You've got heart Krillin,
but face it,
we're not in much of
a condition for Garlic Jr.!
[groans]
No, I... I can beat him!
[KRILLIN] I-If I can keep
Garlic Jr. away from you
until Kami gets back,
then your strength will return.
Until then, I'm all ya got.
Okay. I'm going for it!
[KRILLIN groans]
Huh?
Aah!
[KRILLIN yells]
[GARLIC JR. groans]
[GARLIC JR.]
Why you little bald-headed...
[growls]
Oh yeah?!
Yeah!
[yells]
[growls]
[GARLIC JR.] Come on, cueball!
Let's see what you got!
[yells]
[KRILLIN] Kamehame... Ha!
[chuckles]
So you wanna play catch, huh?
What a curve ball!
--[KRILLIN] Yaaahhh!
--[GAARLIC JR.] Huh?!
[yells]
Can't... give up!
[GARLIC JR. groans]
[groans]
[yells]
Nice try!
[GARLIC JR.] But you'll have
to do a lot better than that!
[GARLIC JR.] Oh you are so dead!
Got any last words?
Say hello to a
whole new world of pain!
No, Krillin!
[yells]
[laughs]
[bellows]
[PICCOLO] Put him down, now!
[GARLIC JR.]
Oh yeah? What if I don't?
What are you going to do?
I could use... a little help...!
Come and get him!
[yells]
[chuckles]
[groans]
[PICCOLO groans]
Yeah... [laughs]
Two heads are
always better than one!
[yelling]
[yells]
[snoring]
[coughing]
[coughs]
[MARON screams]
Uh!
How dare you!
You tried to bite me!
I didn't bite you!
You rolled over
and stuck your foot
in my mouth!
[MARON] Whatever!
I guess you're
not used to having
someone else's
foot in your mouth, huh?
Huh?
[MARON] Hey, look!
We're just in time to see
the sun come up, Yajirobe!
Check it out!
I can't wait!
[laughs]
So what d'ya
think of that, Korin?
[KORIN] That's strange.
The sun shoulda been up
hours ago. Something must be up!
[MARON]
Who's a cute kitty cat?
Yeah, you're a cute kitty.
Cut that out!
[laughing]
[GOHAN] Hey, ugly!
[growls] Gohan!
Now! Blast him!
Uh. But I can't!
[PICCOLO] Come on, Gohan!
What are you waiting for?!
Do it before he gets away!
Do it! Now!
[GOHAN] I... I just don't
know if I can stop him!
[KAMI yelling]
[POPO]
Let me help you, Kami!
Here, hold onto this!
It's up to you to
pour the Sacred Water.
If these guys want me,
they can have me.
Kami, I can't do it!
I'm scared!
They might kill you!
Let's leave here, now!
I can't! You go on! I'm going
to stay here and distract them!
[gasps]
[KAMI yelling]
Don't just stand there,
get moving!
[yells]
What? But Kami...
Forget me! Just go!
Hurry!
[PICCOLO] Gohan!
Take a shot! Come on!
[GOHAN] He's too strong!
I can't stop him!
[KAMI yelling]
Hurry, Mr. Popo! Hurry!
No! I can't, Kami!
[KAMI] Pour the
Sacred Water, Mr. Popo!
Do it!
[yelling]
[yells]
[KAMI groans, yells]
Ha!
[screams]
Aah!
[growls]
You missed me!
[POPO] Oh, Kami! I hope
it's not too late to save him!
Hm? Huh?
[GARLIC JR.] What's happening?
He did it! Good job!
[KAMI groans]
The threat's over! At last!
[growling]
[growls]
My plan!
[GARLIC JR.] You meddling fools
have ruined everything!
I'll make you pay for this!
For what you did
to me and my father!
And this time I'll
finish you off for good!
[groans]
[yells]
[yelling continues]
It's... the Dead Zone!
The Dead Zone
will swallow you up
and keep you for all eternity!
There's no escape!
[GARLIC JR.] I know you
can't hold on much longer!
[laughs]
There's no use in resisting!
Just think, you'll spend
the rest of your lives
in total darkness!
In the Dead Zone!
[GARLIC JR.] At last
I will have my revenge!
[NARRATOR] Garlic Jr.
has done the unthinkable!
He has opened the portal
to the Dead Zone!
And our heroes
will have a tough time
escaping the hungry vortex
that could seal them in
the cold darkness for eternity!
On the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!