[GOKU bellows]
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Goku was stranded
on the planet Namek
when it exploded and
was blown to smithereens!
[NARRATOR]
But Bulma wasn't worried,
because she found out that
the Dragon Balls from Namek
possessed certain
advantages that
the Earth's
Dragon Balls didn't have!
Goku, Krillin, and Chiaotzu
can all be wished back!
[NARRATOR] King Kai, however,
was less than enthusiastic.
[KING KAI] Using the Nameks'
Dragon Balls is a great idea,
but I'm afraid it won't
help Goku and Krillin.
[YAMCHA and CHIAOTZU] Huh?
He brings them back to
the place where they died!
Goku and Krillin died on Namek.
They would materialize in space.
Right where Namek used to be!
[NARRATOR] Is there any hope
to bring our heros back?
Find out, today!
[birds chirping]
[BULMA] Gosh, Goku...
Hey, there's got to be a way.
We just can't give up.
Whadda ya think?
[BULMA] I don't know, Gohan.
King Kai was
pretty clear on the matter.
It's no problem
to wish Chiaotzu back
because he died on Earth.
But I'm afraid it's a
completely different matter
with your dad and Krillin.
There's no nest
to lay the eggs in!
Hey, that's a good analogy!
Yeah, sure.
[BULMA] Your dad
and Krillin are the eggs
and the Dragon is the hen,
but there's no nest
for her to lay her eggs in!
And since there's not
a cozy space for the eggs,
they get cold and crack,
and the little chickies
end up dying.
That's awful. Gosh!
[BULMA] I'm sorry, Gohan.
I know it's hard.
Your dad's a really good egg.
--[VEGETA] Shut up!
--[BULMA] Wha--?!
Enough of this
ridiculous babble!
[gasps]
If you want Kakarot back,
then listen.
The Earth has a Check-in
Station to the spirit realm.
Wish him back there first.
Then wish him back to life.
Hey! That might work!
[BULMA] Man, Vegeta! What a
great idea! I'm impressed!
[grunts]
[BULMA] This is awesome!
We need to gather
the Dragon Balls!
[GOHAN] Uh...
Thank you very much!
[laughs]
[VEGETA]
Don't get carried away!
[grunts]
You bunch of softies!
[BULMA] Huh...?
[VEGETA] Silly fools!
I'm not interested
in helping Kakarot.
I want to know how
he became a Super Saiyan,
so I can do it too!
[MOORI]
Excuse me, Miss Bulma.
We have a request
we'd like to make.
We plan to use our Dragon Balls
to relocate to another planet.
But finding a suitable
home is going to take time.
Do you know of a place
where we can stay temporarily
until we can make
other arrangements.
[BULMA] Gosh...
Hey, I know! Just stay with me!
No. We mustn't impose.
Aw, hey,
it's really no biggie.
It's the least
I can do for you all.
Besides, you need a major
credit card to stay in a hotel.
Huh?
[BULMA] Hey, no worries.
My dad's compound is huge.
There's enough room
for everyone.
It's not like you guys
have a lot of options.
Green men from outer space
aren't a common
sight around here.
Oh, gosh! I see your point.
We... accept.
What about you?!
Hey, homeboy!
Huh? What? Home--what?
Hey, loosen up.
You're going to need
a place to crash, too.
Agh!
[BULMA] Hey, why don't you
drop the arrogant tough-guy act
and just relax. Let it all go!
Take a vacation
for goodness sake.
Unwind a little and see
what life has to offer you.
You're actually kind of cute.
[giggles]
What? I'm not kind of--!
Shut up!
All right then!
It's all settled!
I'm going to go call my dad
and have him pick all of us up.
[MOORI] Thank you so much!
[GOHAN] Bulma?
Um... do you think I could
stay at your house
for a little while?
[BULMA] What are you
talking about, kiddo?
You have your own beautiful
house with a wonderful mom,
who's probably
worried sick about you.
Well, yeah. But...
it'll just be for a short time.
Please? Just 'til
I finish my homework.
[DR. BRIEF] What's the
deal here? Darn thing!
Oh, there!
All right, gang,
everything is a go!
Now remember,
when you first take-off
it's going to feel like
someone's trying to
pull your brains out
through your feet!
But once you clear
the Earth's atmosphere,
you're going to feel
like you're walking on
a cushion of air!
Now everyone, are you ready?!
[ALL grunt]
It's about time! I'm ready
for action! Lock and load!
[DR. BRIEF]
Uh, just a moment.
I have a phone-call
coming in. Please standby.
Uh, sorry. That was Bulma.
She's back on Earth!
She said that Gohan
is with her as well!
Huh?
[DR. BRIEF] Does anyone
still want to go to Namek
or should I cancel the flight?
[ALL yell]
[CHICHI]
Step on it! Oh, come on!
I could walk faster
than this piece of junk!
[whimpers]
Hey, that's them! All right!
Yo! Dad! We're down here!
Gohan! It's Mommy!
Huh? Well, where is he?
Gohan! It's you!
Uh-huh...
[CHICHI] My son!
Yep! That's me...!
Well, guys, this is going to be
your new home for a while.
It's not the Taj Mahal, but
I think you're gonna like it.
Hi! Are you the one
who helped Goku
save my beautiful little girl
from those horrible men?
You should get a medal!
You're a hero!
I... I, uh...
A ship!
She's a real beauty!
Advanced supertronics...
the best!
Self generating
laser powered reactor,
and a stereo system that
will bring the house down!
Not bad. Kakarot must've used
a ship just like this one.
[beep]
Hi, Vegeta. Come on out.
Cold drinks for everyone.
I made you a Shirley Temple.
[NARRATOR] And so began
a period of rest and recreation
for the visitors
from outerspace.
Moori became an expert putter.
[NARRATOR] The Namek boys
learned how to play poker.
[NARRATOR] And a certain frog
became the proud new ruler
of the fish pond.
[NARRATOR]
One hundred and thirty days
seemed to pass by very quickly,
and it was time to summon
the Eternal Dragon once again.
Gosh, are you guys ever lucky.
Our Dragon Balls take a
whole year to regenerate.
Ours too. We Nameks just have
shorter year than you all do.
Oh. Gotcha! Well,
what do you guys think?
I say we should we call
upon the Eternal Dragon
while we're still young.
Are you up to it?
Sure, why not?!
But... where's... Gohan?
[CHICHI]
Hey! Hold on! Wait for us!
Hey! What's up, kid?
[GOHAN] Not a lot!
Sorry we're late.
I had to finish my homework.
[BULMA] Don't sweat it, kid.
You're fashionably late
and that's okay.
Gohan's been hitting
the books a lot lately.
He's almost caught up
on all the work he missed
while he was gone.
Man! What a
little champion! Cool!
Well, Dende? Whadda ya say?
Sure!
[speaking Namekian]
[gasps]
[howls]
[growls]
[PORUNGA growls]
Wow! Now that's a dragon!
Yes! Oh, my! Dear me!
[gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
[screams] It's a monster!
[ALL gasp]
Whoa! Look at
the size of that thing!
Not on my beat!
We're taking that overgrown
lizard downtown, bro!
Go ahead! I'll back ya up!
I have... no clue.
[MAN] This is Sky-Cam Six
with the five o'clock
traffic report!
I quit!
I don't get
paid enough for this!
[OFFICER]
Ladies and gentlemen!
We have traced the origin
of the appararition
to the Capsule Corporation!
Go home. There is
no need to panic.
Aw, man!
[OFFICER] It's just
another one of Dr. Brief's
crazy experiments!
[indistinct chatter]
You who have summoned me.
I will now grant
you three wishes.
Now, proceed with your wishes.
Go ahead, my friends.
We can wait another
hundred and thirty days
to start our new life.
Besides, I think I can
improve my putt.
It's all in the wrist.
And the follow-through.
Well, shoot! Let's do it then!
Please bring Goku and Krillin
to Earth's Check-in Station
in the spirit realm.
[DENDE speaking Namekian]
All right. Just a sec.
[PORUNGA]
The one called Krillin
is at the Earth's
Check-in Station.
--[GOHAN and BULMA sigh]
--[DR. BRIEF] Ah!
But the one called Goku
cannot be brought
to that place.
What? Darn! What's up?!
Why not?
Because he is alive.
If I moved him there now,
he would die.
[CHICHI gasps]
[GOHAN] Dad's really
still alive? But how?
[VEGETA] Kakarot...
What? Goku? Alive? Huh?
--[PUAR laughs, cheers]
--[OOLONG] Hey! Yeah! Ha-ha!
Yay! [laughs]
[GOHAN laughs]
Hey, if Goku's alive, why
hasn't he come back yet? Huh?
[GOHAN] Well, maybe his
ship's broken!
Yeah, I'll bet he's stuck!
My friends! Look!
He's alive, right?
So, just wish him back here.
Hey! Great idea!
Yeah!
[laughs]
Now, the next wish!
Let's bring Krillin
back to life!
[OOLONG and PUAR cheering]
[speaking Namekian]
Huh? What? How?
Welcome back, partner!
[KRILLING] Oh, wow!
Wait a minute...
I'm back alive!
[ALL cheering]
[PORUNGA clears throat]
Hey! Yo, people!
Let's move it! One more wish!
Oooo! Sorry!
You're cute! I like you!
--[BULMA giggles]
--[PORUNGA] Oh...
Uh...
[BULMA] All right, then.
Let's do it.
For the last wish,
let's bring Goku back to Earth!
[cheering, lauhging]
[speaking Namekian]
[PORUNGA growls lowly]
[PORUNGA growls]
Goku...!
[BOTH laugh]
[PORUNGA] Silence!
It can't be done!
Oh...
[PORUNGA] The one called Goku
refuses to return
and says he'll come back later.
What? But, why?
[ROSHI] I know why.
Because he's scared,
that's why!
Of the one more powerful
than a Super Saiyan; his wife!
[CHICHI] What?!
Yikes! No! Please, no!
It was a joke!
Gosh, why doesn't
Dad wanna come back?
[PICCOLO] Your dad told Porunga
that he'll be back later.
Don't worry, Gohan.
He'll keep his word.
[VEGETA] Kakarot!
What are you up to?
You're probably training
on another planet somewhere
perfecting your skills!
While I'm sitting here wasting
my time with these bozos!
[grunts]
[distant rumbling]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
[MRS. BRIEF] Isn't that
your spaceship, darling?
[DR. BRIEF] Well, it was...!
Ohh...
[PICCOLO] Forget about him!
He's gone! No big loss!
Don't you guys have
some friends at King Kai's
that want to come back?
[BULMA] Oh, yeah!
Three of them.
But who should we
wish back first?
[KING KAI] Hey guys!
They want to
wish one of you back,
but you have to choose.
Chiaotzu?
I think I'll stay here
and train some more.
You guys can pick.
Well, if he's staying,
I'm staying, too!
Very well then.
Yamcha, you're up!
[chatters]
Where's bubbles? He's gone!
Well... the hand
is quicker than the eye!
He knows better than that!
[KING KAI]
Bulma, can you hear me?
This is King Kai speaking.
Oh! Gosh, hi, King Kai!
[KING KAI] Bulma,
I asked all the guys
to decide which one
of them would go back first
and they chose Yamcha.
Yamcha, huh? Okay.
He probably
drew the short straw.
I'll bet he cheated.
Hey, Dende. Yamcha's our man.
[speaking Namekian]
[PORUNGA growls]
So be it.
[PORUNGA] It is done.
Your wish has been granted.
It has? But where is he?
[PORUNGA] I have
fulfilled three wishes.
I am finished here.
Uh, no! Wait! Please!
[growls]
Oh man! Bummer...!
The Dragon short-changed us!
No he didn't! I'm over here!
[chuckles nervously]
Ribbit, ribbit!
Yamcha! I missed you!
[laughs]
Puar, easy!
[PUAR]
You're really back!
[BULMA] Yamcha...?
Hey! Wow! You're looking
better than ever, Bulma!
I missed you a lot!
[NARRATOR] One hundred
and thirty days later,
on a sunny afternoon,
a peculiar darkness
overtook the sky once again!
The first wish was
used to bring back
the young Emperor, Chiaotzu.
[cheering and laughing]
[NARRATOR] With the next wish,
Tien was brought back.
Huh?
Are we, uh...?
Mm.
[CHIAOTZU] Oh, Tien! I can't
believe it! We're home!
[sobbing]
[clapping and cheering]
[growls]
[giggles]
Well, Dende...
It's time to say good-bye.
[DENDE] Yes, sir.
Good-bye, friends.
We love each of you.
Gosh! You're so sweet.
Gohan. I'm sorry, but I
have to say good-bye now.
Gosh, Dende.
I promise, I'll never
forget you, Gohan.
All right.
Let's have it already.
[DENDE speaking Namekian]
See ya!
Yeah, see ya!
Gohan...
Bye!
Dende!
[NARRATOR]
And so the star-voyagers
from the planet Namek
left the Earth
to begin life a new
somewhere deep in space!
[OX-KING] ChiChi, is that
meat loaf I smell?
[CHICHI] Yes, Dad.
It's meat loaf.
Mmm! Yummy! I love meat loaf!
[PICCOLO] If you ever
need me, Gohan...
I'll be there for you, kid.
[NARRATOR] At long last,
life returned to normal
for Gohan and his family.
Except that every night,
they would go out and
look at the stars together,
and wonder when the one they
loved would finally return!