[GOKU] Get down, now!
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Frieza's evil plan to dominate
the Universe finally fell apart!
With the planet Namek teetering
on the edge of destruction,
it was time for Goku
to bid Frieza farewell!
[NARRATOR] But the half of
Frieza that Goku left behind
obviously wasn't
his better half!
Unable to accept defeat,
the one-armed, legless villain
bitterly gathered his energy
for a last ditch effort
to hit Goku from behind!
Huh?
[NARRATOR] The Super Saiyan
had had enough though.
Having already spared
Frieza's life twice,
it was time to put an end
to this shameless menace
once and for all!
[screams]
[NARRATOR] But can Goku make it
off Namek before it explodes?
Find out, today!
[distant rumbling]
I can't take this!
Has anything happened, King Kai?
[TIEN]
I've got to know! Please!
[KING KAI] Yes, something
has happened, Tien!
The fight is over!
Frieza is dead!
[ALL gasp]
Frieza was pleading
for his life to Goku,
so Goku tried to help him out!
He gave Frieza
some of his own power!
[KING KAI] But instead of
using the power to escape,
Frieza turned on Goku,
and used it to attack him!
[grunts] Man, what a jerk!
[KING KAI] Indeed! So Goku was
forced to deliver the final blow
to put an end
to the fight for good.
All right! You're saying
that Goku won, right?
Yes, after Goku transformed
into a Super Saiyan,
Frieza found himself
totally outclassed.
Yes!
[YAMCHA and CHIAOTZU laughing]
[TIEN] Oh wow. That means
Goku is the strongest fighter
in the Universe. Whatd'ya know!
Right from our own backyard!
I wouldn't mind a little
sparring session,
just to see how I measure up!
[CHIAOUTZU laughs]
Hold it! Quiet!
[BOTH] Huh?
Goku defeated Frieza
but he didn't win!
As a matter of fact,
he just might lose!
Lose? But how?
By still being on Namek
when it explodes, that's how!
[YAMCHA] Oh.
He doesn't have enough time!
He's heading to
Frieza's spaceship
because it's closer than his!
But Namek could blow
any second now!
The surface looks like
boiling spaghetti sauce.
It would take a miracle
to get him out in time!
[KING KAI] But I haven't
given up hope... not yet!
Hey! Goku's gotten himself
out of some hairy situations!
If there's any way out,
he'll find it!
He's like the great
Houdini or something.
I guarantee,
he'll get out of there!
C'mon! Guys! This is Goku
we're talking about! Lighten up!
[KING KAI] I wish that there
was something to
"lighten up" about!
Uhh... I guess you'd
just have to see it!
[GOKU] There it is! Oh, great!
It looks pretty beat up!
Darn!
[GOKU] Okay now,
where's the bridge?
[GOKU] Oh, man!
I don't think this is it!
[grunts]
[GOKU] I'm getting a
bad feeling about this!
[GOKU panting]
[grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
C'mon, baby! Please work!
[beeping]
All right! Now I just need to
figure out how to make it go.
[GOKU] C'mon, c'mon!
There! That's it!
[engine humming]
Huh?
[GOKU] Aah. It's working!
Come on! Come on!
[GOKU] Huh?
Oh, no, what happened?
It died! Piece of junk!
What now?
[GOKU] Oh, man!
Please work! Come on!
Come on, baby, work for me!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[GOKU] Man o' man! Now what?!
That was my only
ticket outta here!
Eeeeh yow!
[BOTH] Huh?
Aaah! Whoa! That was a doozy!
Oh no! No!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Something's up!
[KING KAI] It's Frieza's ship!
Goku got to it in time,
but it's broken!
What a lemon!
And now it's gone!
Swallowed up by the lava!
[YAMCHA grunts]
Was Goku on it?!
[KING KAI] No! But that was
Goku's only way
to get off of Namek!
He's stuck there now. Alone.
The only soul
on the whole planet,
and it's about to blow!
There's nothing he can
do anymore, guys. It's over.
--[YAMCHA] Goku...
--[CHIAOTZU] Goku...
[GOKU] I won't give up!
I will not give up!
[yells]
[grunts]
It's happening, you guys!
Goku...!
No way!
It can't be... Goku, no!
Oh, no...!
[GOKU yells]
[TIEN] King Kai...?
What happened?!
It's over, isn't it?!
[KING KAI] I think so...
Yes. Let me make sure.
[grunting]
[KING KAI] Just as I feared!
There is no more Planet Namek.
It's gone!
Sorry, you guys. I know
how much you cared about him.
[YAMCHA grunts]
No! Goku!
[YAMCHA]
You sacrificed everything...
Goodness gracious!
I guess I need to
give the bad news to Gohan.
It'll break his heart for sure.
Oh, boy, oh, boy!
How can I tell him?!
You could try breaking
the news through Bulma.
That's not a bad idea.
I can tell her, King Kai.
I'm close to Bulma.
[KING KAI] So be it, Yamcha.
Come forward.
You know the score.
Right.
[KING KAI]
Whenever you're ready, Yamcha.
[YAMCHA] Okay, here goes!
[YAMCHA]
Bulma! Can you hear me?!
[BULMA] Huh?! Who said that?
I must be losing my mind!
[YAMCHA] Bulma, you're not
losing your mind.
It's me, Yamcha.
Huh? Yamcha. Where?
I don't see you.
[ALL] Huh?
[BULMA] I can hear you though.
Did somebody
shrink you or something?
[YAMCHA] No. Nobody
shrunk me. I'm full-sized.
Look, Bulma. I'm communicating
with you telepathically!
King Kai arranged it.
I'm relaying a message for him.
No way!
Bulma, Yamcha's talking to you?
It's King Kai!
He must have a message!
Hey, that's what he said!
Man, that's wild!
Telepathy, huh? So it's
true then. It is Yamcha.
Hi-ya, Yamcha! What's up?
[YAMCHA]
Notta lotta! Just hanging out
with the other dead guys.
You know how it is.
[YAMCHA] But, hey,
I have to hurry because, uh,
I'm sort of
calling long distance.
It's about Goku, Bulma.
The fight on Namek is over.
[BULMA]
You're kidding. Who won?!
[YAMCHA] Goku did!
He beat Frieza! But, uhh...
Goku won?! All right!
That's our Goku!
Hey, guys! Goku won!
Wow! Dad really won?!
Yay! Wooo!
[GOHAN and DENDE laughing]
[PICCOLO]
Goku! You did it, my friend!
[chuckles]
[laughing]
[VEGETA]
He did it?! Unbelievable!
[YAMCHA] Bulma, please, listen!
That's not the end of
the story. There's more.
After Goku defeated Frieza,
he tried to use
Frieza's spaceship
to high-tail it out of there.
But the darn thing
bugged out on him.
He was stuck!
With no way out!
When Namek exploded,
Goku went with it! He's gone.
Hold on, guys! There's more!
[BULMA] Goku didn't make it off
Planet Namek before it exploded.
--[BULMA] He's dead.
--[YAMCHA] Huh?!
[BULMA] What a bummer!
[YAMCHA]
Bulma, what are you doing?!
Are you nuts?! You're not
giving a weather report
or announcing the score
of a football game!
The kid's dad just died!
I could have done
a better job than that!
[lauhging]
Duh! Now listen up, pea brain!
I'm the one with the
real inside scoop, not you.
What would you say
if I told you that
with the Dragon
Balls from Namek,
you can wish people back to
life more than just one time.
That means that we can
wish everybody back.
Goku, Krillin, and Chiaotzu
can all be wished back!
[BULMA] You're all coming home!
How do you like them apples?!
And it's not going to
take that long either!
So just chill! You dork!
I was always the brains of the
outfit when we were together,
and you were always the brawn.
[YAMCHA]
Oh, man! Same ol' Bulma.
Yamcha. What's up?!
[TIEN] What's going on?!
It looks like we're goin' home!
Hey, Chiaotzu,
that means you too!
Me?!
What's the deal?!
[KING KAI] Using the Nameks'
Dragon Balls is a great idea,
but I'm afraid it won't
help Goku and Krillin.
[TIEN] Why not?!
Well, when the Dragon
restores someone's life,
he brings them back to
the place where they died.
But Goku and Krillin
died on Namek.
Oh, I get it now.
Namek isn't there.
Yes, you hit the nail
on the head. Namek's gone.
What a shame.
It was a great idea.
But can we try it anyway?!
Of course you can, but I
already know what would happen.
Trust me, it's not something
you'd want to do
to your friends.
[KING KAI] They would
materialize in space...
Right where Namek used to be.
And die a lonely death
in the middle of nowhere.
[gasps]
King Kai! There must be
something you can do!
Can't you use your powers
to help them?!
I wish I could.
I'd gladly step in
if it was within my power!
[KING KAI]
I'm sorry, guys. Really.
What's wrong, Bulma?
You look sad.
King Kai... he said...
that Goku can't come back...
[BOTH gasp]
I-If we wished them back,
they would go to
the planet Namek,
but the planet Namek's gone.
Dad?! No way!
You're gone for good?!
[PICCOLO] I'm sorry, Gohan.
[VEGETA laughs]
I told you, didn't I?!
It looks like my prophecy
came to pass after all.
I'm number one now, guys.
So get used to it.
It was nice of your dad, kid.
[VEGETA] Getting rid
of Frieza like that for me.
What a guy!
He served his purpose.
Jerk! You're nothing
compared to him!
He spared your life twice!
He shouldn't have
been so soft, should he?
Which leads me to the question
of what to do with his son.
[VEGETA] Destroy him now, so he
doesn't destroy me someday?!
Don't sweat it, kiddo.
You're the only
Saiyan left besides me.
That makes you a
very important young man.
We're the last survivors
of an Ancient race.
[VEGETA] Besides, I need
someone like you at my side
to polish my boots
and call me Lord Vegeta.
[laughs]
My dad'll be back, you watch!
You're dad is history, kid!
[yells, groans]
Hm!
Hey, you leave him alone, jerk!
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
Are you challenging me, kid?
I wouldn't recommend it.
It's your call. Go ahead!
My dad will take care of you!
And he will be back!
[yells]
[GOHAN yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[yells]
[VEGETA coughs]
[BULMA] Gohan!
[groans]
[VEGETA] All right, kid,
that does it!
If you want to challenge the
Prince of all Saiyans, you can!
But I promise,
this fight will be your last!
[panting]
You're making a big mistake.
[yells]
[VEGETA] Where do
you think you're going?
Hmm?
[VEGETA grunting]
[GOHAN groaning]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Oh, no! Gohan's
in serious trouble!
Gohan, no!
[PICCOLO] Hang in there, kid.
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[screams]
[VEGETA] Pity!
What a waste of talent.
Bye.
Hm?
Not today! Back off!
[VEGETA scoffs]
Ah... Have it your way.
Please... Father...
Come home...
I know you're
still up there somewhere.
You have to be.
I need you, Dad...!
[grunts]
A tough guy like you should
be able to face the truth!
[DENDE] Are you, okay?
I don't see how you did it.
Father...
Goku...
[BULMA] Goku!
[NARRATOR] The planet
Namek finally exploded
and has disappeared
without a trace!
And Goku is gone as well!
Is the pure-hearted savior
really just a memory now?
Find out, on the next
Dragon Ball Z!