[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the misfit cavalry arrived!
Leaping from their
bedazzled pink helicopter,
Mr. Satan's top two students
entered the Cell Games
to fight in their
master's place.
First came the graceful
and self-proclaimed
ladies' man Caroni.
He launched into the
air with his signature
"Beautiful Flying Rose Attack."
And with a little
boost from Cell's energy,
it was indeed a finishing
move... for Caroni.
[CARONI whimpers]
[NARRATOR] Next was
muscle-man Pirozhki,
who charged Cell with his prized
move, the Megaton Bull Crusher!
[NARRATOR] But without
lifting a finger,
Cell bowled over
the bulbous fighter
with a mere exertion
of his energy!
[PIROZHKI grunting]
[NARRATOR] That's two for Cell,
none for planet Earth!
[PIROZHKI groans]
[NARRATOR] Annoyed by
his students' slip-ups,
Mr. Satan stepped in
to settle the score.
It was time for the
World Champion of Martial Arts
to show his stuff.
[MR. SATAN grunting]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] With Mr. Satan's
mouth finally shut,
Cell could actually begin
the tournament he'd intended.
[CELL] Let's get this
tournament underway.
Who will be first?
Will it be Goku
to start things off?
[NARRATOR] Goku, who had been
anxiously waiting for his chance
to square off with Cell, had
only one thing to say:
[GOKU] Let's do it.
[NARRATOR] At last,
the main event has come!
In one corner,
the biological android
created only to destroy.
And in the other, the greatest
hero the Earth has ever known.
The fight begins... today!
L-Ladies and gentlemen,
our last hope rested upon
the shoulder's of Mr. Satan.
But now that he's lost, does
this mean... we're all doomed?
This should be good.
Yeah...
[VEGETA thinking] All right,
Kakarot...
It's time to see
what you can do!
[CELL] As I'm sure
you know by now,
I've been waiting for this!
Killing the helpless
quickly grows old.
[CELL chuckles softly]
[CELL] I'm counting on you for
amusement while I test my body.
I hear you're designed to use
all of our techniques
against us.
Perfection.
[MR. SATAN groans]
[ANNOUNCER] Hmm?
What? Mr. Satan!
[groaning continues]
May I ask what happened
with you there in the ring?
Hey, it's no big deal!
I just lost my footing!
You... lost your... footing?
[MR. SATAN] Yes, I did!
But it looked... like you
were launched from the ring!
Sure, it looked that
way to an untrained eye!
But you're forgetting
Hercule's strength!
I mean, when your
big bulging muscles
can make tin foil
out of a tour bus,
the smallest slip will
send you flying for miles!
Huh? Is that a fact?
[BOTH] It is fact!
O-kay...
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
Don't worry!
Once I take a short break
to re-lace my boots,
I'll get back in there
and squash that wimp!
Now who rules?!
[PIROZHKI &amp; CARONI]
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
That ridiculous man
hasn't realized his weakness!
His stupidity's beyond belief!
[HERCULE laughs]
[TRUNKS thinking] So this is it.
Now we'll see why Goku's
been acting so confident
all this time.
Folks if you're just
tuning in there's great news!
Just moments ago,
Mr. Satan confided in me
he simply lost
his footing in the ring!
So once he ties his shoes,
he'll be back for more!
In the meantime,
we might as well get another
preliminary bout over with.
This time Cell's challenger
will be that cocky guy
with the big hair!
But don't go too far
away from your sets, folks,
because this little
skirmish shouldn't take long!
In my professional opinion,
this could get pretty
ugly for the guy.
Hercule, any
comments on the fight,
or maybe some advice
for the challenger?
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
Just by looking at the runt,
all I gotta say is ya
better have a stretcher
and an ambulance standing by!
Goku is just awesome!
[TIEN] His form, it's flawless!
Just look at him...
he's standing right
in front of Cell
like it's just another
day at the beach.
Yeah, it would almost appear
like he's enjoying the moment.
With all this new control
as a Super Saiyan,
he's by far the best
chance this planet has.
Well, if I were
fighting that twerp,
I'd bend him into a pretzel
and eat him for lunch!
But, lucky for him,
I'm on a strict diet!
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
Enough joking.
Here's my prediction:
In five seconds, that
kid's gonna be history!
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
I sure hope he's
got a health plan!
But, really, it's good
that he's fighting
because it'll make my
fight look even better!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Ding!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU yelling]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[GOKU] Hmph.
[BOTH whimpering]
[gasping]
Their strength
appears to be equal.
And so far, it looks
like neither of them
are even short of breath!
The challenger seems to be
stronger than we thought...
Now, with his expert
analysis, here's Mr. Satan...
Your thoughts
on the fight so far?
Ahh... Your thoughts?
Uhh...
What, do you think
of the fight so far?
Oh, yeah... Fight! Ah, right!
I think it's a good fight, but
I would beat both of them
with one hand tied
behind my back.
[MR. SATAN laughs nervously]
[BOTH gasp]
[CELL grunts]
Look, he's out!
He's right!
Huh...?
Sorry, but did you think
you had defeated me?
Ha! I won't fall
for your cheap pranks!
I knew all along
that it wouldn't be that
easy to take you out, Cell!
I thought it'd be appropriate
to play a little joke
since you aren't
fighting me seriously.
Hey, you're
holding back as well.
Little by little,
I shall reveal to you...
the perfect power
that lies within me!
Bring it on!
You seem to be enjoying
yourself very much.
I'm not surprised.
As a Saiyan, fighting
is all you live for.
Are you saying
you're any different?
[CELL chuckles]
It depends on who I'm fighting.
Well, then...
I'll try not to disappoint you.
Where'd they go?
Huh?!
[BOTH gasp]
I've never seen
anything like this!
They keep disappearing!
It's just a cheap
optical illusion!
I've seen it before, see...
It's all done with mirrors.
That's amazing!
Wow, Hercule, with all
your genius and knowledge, why,
I bet you could do
the same thing if you wanted,
like RIGHT NOW if you wanted!
But, I can't...
seem to figure out where
they've hidden the mirrors.
Can you, Hercule? Huh!?
Hey! Where did
you go, Mr. Satan?
Don't you realize
we're live on the air?!
Don't do this to me!
Come out, come out
where ever you are!
Ladies and gentlemen,
I can't explain it,
but the champ has vanished!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Alright, Hercule,
where were you?
As you and your television
audience have just witnessed,
I, too, am a master
of optical illusion!
Oh, yeah, that's right!
[ANNOUNCER] Man alive!
You really had me stumped!
Where'd he get the material
for that gorgeous cape?
I saw he and Piiza
sewing it up last night!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] These doorknobs
are cracking me up!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Krillin!
I'm sorry...
Their speed, it's incredible!
I can't keep up!
[VEGETA thinking] Ha!
So you think that's fast?
Wait until you see me!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[PICCOLO growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
It looks like those
two are back at it again.
This is just what
gives fighting a bad name!
[CELL chuckles]
Goku!
[blows landing]
Ohh, I see them now!
Like I said,
they were just hiding!
[gasping]
You feel that terrific force?!
That's the same thing I felt
when he knocked me
from the ring!
Yes, same here.
There's something most
very strange going on here.
They keep on cheating with
these second-grade illusions!
They clearly have no respect
for the Martial Arts!
Goku!
The edge of the ring!
It looks like Cell's in control!
But how come?
How come Dad isn't
taking this seriously?
What?
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA thinking] Well,
well... Just as I thought!
Kakarot and Cell are simply
having sport with one another!
[CELL chuckles]
Oh, you're good.
[GOKU] Kaa... Mee...
Haa... Mee...
[GOKU] Haaaaa!
[CELL gasps]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[CELL yells]
[CELL growls]
[GOKU grunts]
Alright, I suppose that
was a good enough warm-up.
Yeah.
Huh?
That was
just their warm-up?!
Well, it looks
like they're ready
to get down to it for real!
[GOKU thinking] He's just
as strong as I imagined,
and that means
I've gotta be on edge.
One slip, and it'll
be all over...
[gasping]
[GOKU growls]
Now!
[TRUNKS thinking] Hey,
what's going on?
Goku, what are you up to?
[CELL thinking] Yes,
now we will see!
[BOTH whimpering]
[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
The practice runs are over,
and Goku is ready to exert his
true power as a Super Saiyan.
Will Goku finally reveal the
secret to his confidence?
Does he in fact have the
power to defeat the evil Cell?
What new powers
did Goku discover
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber?
The answers are soon to come,
as the deep strengths
hidden inside our hero
are rising to the top!
Don't miss the
boiling point,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!