[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragonball Z,
Cell continued his
campaign of terror
carving a path of destruction
by draining the life force
from anyone who got in his way.
Krillin found out first hand
Cell's awesome power
when he went
head-to-head with him
and ended up
trapped and helpless.
Luckily, Piccolo and Tien showed
up just in the nick of time
to chase the android
creature away.
The whole experience left
Krillin a little drained,
but it could have
been a lot worse.
[CHICHI] Goku? What?
[NARRATOR] ChiChi was surprised
to find Goku out of bed
and even more surprised
to see that he was back
to his old self again.
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] That's right, Goku
has made a full recovery,
but there's no time
to celebrate.
[GOKU] Hey, I'm alright.
Just relax now...
It's time for me to start
my training once again.
There's a level beyond
that of a Super Saiyan.
Huh?
[NARRATOR] Is Goku
still running a fever?
What is he talking about?
[GOKU] And I will
rise to claim it!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU chuckles]
Yeah, I plan on being
stronger than a Super Saiyan!
[ROSHI yelps]
What's that?! Did you say
stronger than a Super Saiyan?!
I don't think it
can be done!
[ROSHI grunts]
I can do it!
It's the only way to beat Cell.
And I won't know
if I don't try! Will I?
A year...
To know for sure,
a year's all I'll need.
[ROSHI squeals]
A year?
But that's a long time!
Sure it is! But we
both know a place
where it could
be done in a day!
[ROSHI] Hmm...?
[CHICHI growls]
Hey, ChiChi, I'd like
to take Gohan with me
if that's okay with you!
That's a joke, right? Right...?
[GOKU gasps]
Well... What do you
think I'll say, Goku?
[CHICHI growls]
Huh? Yeah! Go ahead.
I can't stop you.
But I want you to make sure
Gohan gets as
strong as possible.
...'Kay?
[GOKU] Sure!
Now, if I let Gohan
go and battle those
androids with you,
you have to promise to let him
study when he gets back alright?
[ROSHI thinking] Hmm...
Interesting.
ChiChi never lets Gohan
put down the books .
This must be some
kind of a trick.
--[CHICHI giggles]
--[ROSHI gasps]
I want you and Gohan
to give it all you've got!
Thanks, ChiChi...
[thinking] I could never deny
you anything, you big lug!
[CHICHI] Goku, I don't
what I'd do without you.
That's sweet...
[ROSHI stammers]
Well, see you!
[kissing sound]
[GOKU] I'll miss you, ChiChi...
[CHICHI] I'll miss you too...
[GOKU grunts]
[ROSHI gasps]
He disappeared!
How'd he do that?!
Come back... soon.
Are we there yet, Yamcha?
[YAMCHA] Soon.
Well, hurry up!
We don't want Cell
to get away again!
We have to stop him...
And quickly!
[PICCOLO] But we have
to find him first.
Aww... We sure need Goku...
--Now!
--Wha--?!
--That'd be really nice...
--It's my... Dad!
Goku?!
Sure would be great
if he'd show up.
It's Daddy!
Goku? Huh?
Hey!
Yup, I must be losing it.
I'm starting to see things!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Goku?
Hi, Krillin!
Goku!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[GOKU] Whoa!
[laughing continues]
Goku! You came back!
[GOKU laughs]
[KRILLIN] Uh-oh...
There goes our ride.
[TIEN] Hey, Yamcha, swing her
around and grab those two!
[KRILLIN] I can't believe it!
[GOHAN sighs]
You're back!
Yeah. So when do we eat?
--Goku! You nut!
--[GOKU laughs]
You're back to
normal alright!
Well... A guy's
gotta eat, right?
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU] Hmm?
[whimpering continues]
[GOKU] Hey, why
the long face, kiddo?
There...
[GOHAN chuckles]
[GOHAN] I missed you, Daddy!
Kamiccolo!
[PICCOLO gasps]
Huh?
[GOKU] What? Did I
say something wrong?
Listen, I've been
through some changes.
But my name is still Piccolo.
And don't forget that!
Sure thing.
No problem!
--Well, what?!
--[GOKU laughs]
Uh... Hey, Piccolo...
There's no way that we can
defeat a power like Cell
in fight right now.
That's why I decided
to start training again.
And I know a place
where I can get a year
of training in a day!
Where is that?
[GOKU] It's at Kami's place!
So it's back to the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber.
I see...
No one has ever been able to
stay there for more than a year.
No one. It might be way more
than you can handle, Goku.
Yeah. That's why I'm
taking Trunks and Vegeta.
Surely one of us
will be able to do it.
Then go, quickly!
Cell gets stronger everyday.
And time is in short supply.
If we let Cell absorb 17,
we're finished for sure!
True. Come on, Gohan!
[GOHAN] Huh?
[GOKU] Take my hand!
Right! Let's do it!
[GOKU grunts]
Wait. Before you go!
[GOKU] Hmm?
Hey! Is it true you guys will
be gone for just one day?
That's cool. Train
hard. We'll find Cell.
It's a deal.
[PICCOLO thinking] One day
is more than we can afford.
It better be worth it!
Things are looking up! When
those guys are done training
I know we'll be
ready for Cell.
[KRILLIN] You bet!
We'll win. And the Earth
will be safe once again!
Man, I just can't wait
to get to Cell now!
His days of terrorizing people
will be over for good!
[thinking] Yes! I can feel it!
I know it can be done!
I can ascend beyond
a Super Saiyan!
The only question is--How?
[thinking] Father!
You're so proud and arrogant!
Well, I've got news for you:
I'm not going anywhere!
If you can raise your power to
the next level, then so can I!
I'm here to stay whether
you like it or not!
[TRUNKS gasps]
Go... ku?
[GOKU] Hey, how's the
training going, Trunks?
[TRUNKS grunts]
Not well...
I guess my father really doesn't
want me to train with him.
He thinks I'll slow him down
and every time I get close
he tells me to get lost!
Look at him! He's
not doing anything!
He's been standing
in the same spot,
staring into space for
the last three days!
He hasn't moved!
Yeah, that is strange...
Maybe he's just
waiting for a sign
or something to
show him the way. Right?
[TRUNKS] Huh?
[GOKU] I'll go have
a word with him.
Hey! Vegeta!
Kakarot,
leave me alone.
Hey, hold on.
I just want to
help you out, Vegeta!
I know what you're
trying to do!
There's a room at Kami's place
where you can get a year
of training in one day!
[VEGETA] Hmm...
I could ascend to the
next level very quickly...
Take me there.
[GOKU] Sure, but
here's theproblem:
Only two people can
go in the room at once.
I'm going in with Gohan, so
you'll have to go with Trunks.
[VEGETA] This better not be
another one of your tricks!
[GOKU] Hey, would I lie to you?
We're all in this
together now, remember?
This is on the level, I promise!
[VEGETA] Alright, I'll go!
As long as I get to go first!
Sure!
[GOKU] You know, this is a
great way for a father and son
to get to know each other.
[ANDROID 18] Hmm...
What do we have here?
Ugh! Rubbish!
Maybe this one?
Eww, no. I don't think so.
How 'bout this one?
Hmmmm...
Whoever owns these clothes
should have their optic
sensors adjusted.
They are obviously
malfunctioning.
No thanks.
Just look at this place...
What a dump.
I can't believe Goku
actually lives here.
[ANDROID 17] 18!
Any sign of Goku in there?
[ANDROID 18] No.
The house is empty.
Goku's friends must have
warned him that we were coming.
[ANDROID 17] Hmph.
He's gone.
[ANDROID 18] Great.
[ANDROID 17] Can you track him
and find his latest location?
It is difficult,
but I will try...
He has moved some
distance from this location.
My tracking mechanism has
not detected his movements
for the last two hours.
Okay. Tell us what you know.
Alright. Goku, was last detected
on a small island to the south.
[ANDROID 17] Then that's
where we will go.
You're the boss.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL laughs]
[COUPLE panting]
[WOMAN screams]
[COUPLE gasps]
[COUPLE screams]
[CELL growls]
[COUPLE whimpers]
[COUPLE screams]
[CELL laughs]
[PICCOLO thinking] They didn't
deserve such a horrible fate...
[YAMCHA sighs]
[YAMCHA] These poor people
never had a chance...
[TIEN whimpers]
[KRILLIN growls]
Darn it! We're always
just one little step behind!
[PICCOLO gasps]
It's Cell!
[CELL] Look at those insects...
I could squash them now,
but I will wait...
I find them very entertaining.
[CELL chuckles]
Please follow me.
You will find everything
you need here...
There's food, a bed, and bath.
It is not very luxurious,
I'm afraid.
I require nothing more
than the essentials.
This is not a vacation,
this is work!
[GOKU] Ignore him, Mr. Popo.
he's a little uptight today.
He's just eager to
complete his training.
Yes, so then I can
take care of you!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[MR. POPO] Here it is.
[GOHAN] Wow! So that's the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber, huh?
[MR. POPO] Alright.
Which group goes first?
Hey! You two, go on in.
Good. Right this way, please.
[MR. POPO] Once you
cross the threshold,
you are to spend a
year in the room.
But when you leave, only
a day will have passed
in this dimension.
Good luck.
[TRUNKS] Hmm...
Thank you, Goku.
[GOKU] Good luck, Trunks.
Take care of Vegeta, okay?
[VEGETA growls]
[GOKU chuckles]
I hope those
two get along...
[VEGETA] What's so
special about this place?
It's hot.
There's less air.
And the gravity is different.
[VEGETA] Hmm...
What?! I don't believe it!
[VEGETA] Hm?
[TRUNKS] There's
nothing here!
We're surrounded
by total emptiness!
We're floating in a
gigantic void!
[TRUNKS] What kind
of a place is this?
[VEGETA] Too much for you?
Of course not. But...
Now, I know why few can stand a
whole year in this place.
It's overwhelming!
It is. It is...
[TRUNKS] I must not let my
Father see that I am afraid...
This is my chance to
prove myself to him!
But I don't know if I can spend
an entire year in this place...
It's too much for me...
It's too much!
[YAMCHA] If we can't sense Cell,
then where is he? He's hiding!
Right?
That's what he does. And the
world's a big place to hide in.
So what?! Then we'll just
get out there and find him!
And fast!
If we don't, Cell will take
total control of this world!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO] We can
chase Cell all we want,
but we're going to need Goku,
Vegeta, Gohan and Trunks
to complete their training and
transform into Ascended Saiyans
if we're going to beat him!
[REPORTER ] If you're planning
on going outside today, don't!
The creature sightings
are at an all-time high.
It would be a good day to
stay in, and lock your doors.
These are dangerous times,
folks, and we can only hope
that somewhere there is someone
--who can stop this monster!
--[PICCOLO] I can't stand it!
Sitting here doing nothing
while Cell continues
his reign of terror!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO] Curse you, Cell!
[PICCOLO] Hn?!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[ANDROID 17] Hi...
Can Goku come out and play?
[thinking] Oh, this is perfect!
It's exactly what I
wanted for breakfast!
Goku is not here.
Not here?
[PICCOLO] Get up!
We have company!
[KRILLIN] Huh...? What...?
What's going on?
This better be good...
[PICCOLO] Stand your
ground! I'll handle this!
Goku's not here, but perhaps
I could take his place.
No thanks... But...
Tell us where he is and
I might change my mind!
[KRILLIN] Oh no!
I don't like the look of this!
Goku's gone now...
So, why don't you go get lost?
Now, now.
It's not very nice to talk to
your guests that way, you know.
Uh-oh! They look like
trouble with a capital T!
Alright. Have it your way.
There. That island.
You and me.
[ANDROID 17] Very well.
If you really want to.
You three stay here.
This is my fight now!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
[ANDROID 18 giggles]
Does Piccolo
have a chance?
No way! The odds
are against him!
No, he can do it!
He has to, at least
until Goku gets back!
Come on, Piccolo!
You can do it Piccolo!
[ANDROID 16] Hm?
[ANDROID 18] I think it's
my turn to sit this one out.
[ANDROID 18 sighs]
[ANDROID 17] If you cooperate.
I'll go easy on you.
[ANDROID 17 sighs]
[ANDROID 17] Last chance.
Tell me where Goku is.
No. Go find him yourself!
[NARRATOR] It looks like Piccolo
has thrown down the gauntlet.
Since uniting with Kami,
he's more powerful
than he's ever been.
But does he have the strength
to beat Android 17?
This could get messy, so don't
miss the next exciting episode
of DragonBall Z!