[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Now Dragon Balls,
grant me my wish!
[NARRATOR] With all seven
Dragon Balls in his possession,
Frieza's victory
seemed certain!
However, making a
wish proved to be
more difficult
than expected...
Maybe it already
came true.
No! There must be some secret
to unlocking their power!
[NARRATOR] As Frieza
raced off in search
of the information he needed,
elsewhere, Gohan was
fighting for his life
and the lives of his friends
against the sinister Recoome!
[GOHAN] No...
It's not over... Yet...
I'm not gonna
let you win!
Now... Here's your doom!
[BOTH grunt]
[NARRATOR] But despite
his most valiant efforts,
the young warrior proved no
match for the towering Recoome.
[NARRATOR] With Gohan
down for the count,
it looked like our heroes'
chances for survival
had finally run out...
When suddenly...
[NARRATOR] A lone spaceship
appeared in the skies,
and came rocketing down
to the planet's surface!
But if the new arrival wasn't
one of Frieza's henchmen,
who else
could it be?
Maybe some Nameks?
Poor dopes! They
shoulda stayed gone...
[NARRATOR] No...
This was no Namek...
The Ginyu Force
will have to contend
with the might
of Goku! Today!
[KING KAI] Huh?!
Hm?
[KING KAI] He made it!
Goku's there!
The others are still in
trouble, but if he hurries,
there may be hope
for them yet!
It's a slim
hope, granted.
But if there's anyone who
can save them, it's Goku!
Yes...
[COMPUTER] Attention.
Landing complete.
Welcome to
Planet Namek.
Passengers are now free
to move about the cabin.
Please watch your step
as you exit the craft,
and as always, thank you
for flying Capsule Corp.
What the...? Who
the heck is that?
[KRILLIN laughs]
It's Goku! I knew it...
I knew he'd make it!
[thinking] Wow...
I'm sensing some really
big powers out there.
Evil powers...
Hang on, guys...
Gohan, Krillin, Bulma...
[thinking] Hmm... Over there.
That's the biggest one...
[thinking] And there's number
two, the second strongest!
But what about
Gohan and Krillin?
Why can't I sense
where they are?
Huh? That's why!
They're barely alive!
Their power...
It's almost down to zero!
I had no idea that I
was cutting it so close!
There's not another
minute to spare!
[GOKU growls]
All right then...
This is it!
It's finally time
to see if all that
100-times gravity
training paid off!
[BOTH gasp]
[JEICE] I don't like
the way this feels!
What the
heck is it?!
[RECOOME yells]
[RECOOME yelling]
[RECOOME gasps]
Gohan...
Hah... Kakarot. Of course...
So he finally
decided to show up...
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[KRILLIN] Goku!
[GOKU] Hey, Krillin!
I brought you a surprise!
Hold on! I'll
be right there!
It's okay, son.
I'm here now...
Gohan?
Hey, son?
Oh, wow... You're
in really bad shape.
But, we can fix that...
You hear me, son?
You're going to be fine,
Gohan, don't you worry!
Hmph! He-Hey! Who the hell
do you think you are?!
You can't just
barge in here!
[GOKU] Try to
swallow this, Gohan.
[RECOOME] Hey! Hello?!
I'm talkin' to you!
This guy's pretty
good, Burter!
That's quite an
entrance he made...
He's really fast!
Maybe even faster than you!
Yeah, right!
Give me a break!
See, low fighting power!
He's all show!
You're too easily
impressed, Jeice!
[GOHAN gasps]
Hey! How do
you feel?!
Daddy? Oh! Dad!
Is it really you?
[RECOOME gasps]
Hey... I thought you said
that kid's neck was broken!
Yeah, well...
It was!
[GOKU] Your mom'd kill me if
she saw how dirty you are.
[GOHAN] Dad! Those guys
are super-powerful!
[GOKU] I know. We definitely
have our work cut out for us.
But I'm here now. Just leave
everything to me, okay?
Yeah... sure...
[GOKU] So, you were taking on
that big guy over there, huh?
[GOHAN] Well, I tried.
But he was too strong for me.
[VEGETA growls]
Vegeta looks like he's
in pretty bad shape, too.
What happened
to him?
The big guy... Vegeta tried
to fight him before I did...
So did Krillin. But they
couldn't beat him either.
[GOKU] Really? Sounds like
this guy's a real handful...
Yeah...
I'll say...
[GOKU laughs]
Don't worry... I've got
just what the doctor ordered!
See? A Senzu Bean!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
I'm so glad
you came...
But I almost
wish you hadn't...
Why, what's
the matter?
[KRILLIN] Those Ginyu guys.
They're just too powerful...
Whaaa?!
It's like he just touches
them and their healed!
Yeah... It's crazy!
Who is this guy?
Curse you...
Kakarot...
[KRILLIN] I'm not
trying to be negative...
It's just, well, I think
we're a little outclassed!
I know you're
really strong...
But, man!
I'm telling you!
We've never dealt with
anything like this!
These guys
are too much!
That's why I say I wish
you hadn't come, Goku...
Now they're just
gonna get you, too!
I mean, Vegeta couldn't
even stop 'em,
and he's
stonger than ever!
Yeah, about Vegeta...
Uhhh...
What was Vegeta doing fighting
them in the first place?
I thought he was
on their side...
I don't know
where to begin!
It's been
crazy here!
[GOKU] Don't speak.
This'll be a lot faster.
Just relax...
[KRILLIN] Oh,
well... Alright.
[GOHAN] Wh-what
are you doing, Dad?
[GOKU] I'm going to
read Krillin's mind...
Thanks...
I understand
everything...
How?
I'm not really sure!
That was my first time!
It's weird! I finished
my training program
on the ship and
something happened...
I didn't think it was any
big deal at the time,
but I guess exercising at
one-hundred times normal gravity
has its benefits!
What?! A hundred times?!
How is that possible?
You'd be crushed!
Nah. I guess I must have
tough skin or something...
I feel just fine!
Well, I'm really
proud of you guys
for everything you've done
so far... What an ordeal.
Until I saw
your thoughts,
I didn't realize just how
much of a struggle
it's been
for you two!
Yeah, thanks.
We... We tried our best
not to let you down...
[GOKU] Aw, neither of you
could ever let me down.
Now, if you'll excuse me
for a second, you guys...
There's a little
something I have to do.
Vegeta!
[BOTH gasp]
Eat it,
Vegeta!
Yo! Hey! We can't be sure
about Vegeta! Are you nuts?!
Why'd you
do that?
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA gasps]
Unbelievable...
My body!
Listen, Goku! I hope
you know what you're doing,
because I sure don't!
You're taking a huge risk!
I owed Vegeta
a favor...
If it wasn't for him,
that guy who freezes time
would have
finished you guys!
Yeah, well, I guess
you've got a point there...
Don't mind me!
Hey, wait! Where
are you going now?
To teach these
Ginyu guys a lesson!
What?! You're gonna
take 'em on by yourself?
[GOKU] I'll be fine...
Be careful...
[BOTH chuckle]
[RECOOME chuckles]
You must think you're some
really hot stuff, huh?
You're gonna beat
us all by yourself, huh??!
Aw, man... What the
heck is Goku thinking?
That hundred-times gravity
must've crushed his brain!
This is crazy.
It's suicide!
I... I don't
know, Krillin...
Dad does seem...
different, somehow...
[RECOOME laughs]
This is turnin' out to
be a really fun day!
Hey! How about
gettin' a reading
on this little punk's
power level, you guys?
Heh. Yeah, right!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Don't sweat it!
It's only five thousand!
Ah! Aw, man, that
really bums me out...
You're just like the
rest... All talk...
I'm not even gonna
have to try.
[VEGETA] Those fools!
They can't sense that
Kakarot is hiding
some of his
fighting ability!
But how much?
Surely Kakarot senses how
powerful these guys are!
And yet he's
perfectly calm...
What could
he be hiding?
No... Is he...
C-Could he be?!
All right. Let's
do this, tough guy.
This is what I
think of you
and your puny
5,000 power level.
[BOTH whimper]
[RECOOME laughs]
Heh.
[door opens]
[BULMA] ChiChi,
please, wait a second!
[CHICHI] Don't you
wait a second me!
I've waited
long enough!
Right!
Is this it?!
I want you to get
on this thing
and call Gohan,
this instant!
Well, I'll try...
But I think it
would be best
if we calmed down
a little bit first...
I am calm!
Oh, right...
[DR. BRIEF] Come in...
Come in, Bulma, do you read?
[BULMA] Huh...?
[DR. BRIEF] Earth to
Bulma... Come in, dear!
[BULMA] Oh, thank
goodness! It's Dad!
Dad, it's me! Hey!
[DR. BRIEF] Bulma?!
Just what the
heck is going on?!
Why isn't Goku
here yet?!
You promised me
he'd be here by now!
[DR. BRIEF] Take it easy,
dear. I'm being
yelled at from both sides!
Let me double check
my calculations...
Now... Where's
that gala--
[CHICHI]
Give me that thing!
[CHICHI &amp; DR. BRIEF grunting]
It's ChiChi!
[CHICHI] Bulma?! Is that
you?! Where's Gohan?!
What have you done
with him?! Tell me!!
Stop yelling at me!
I don't know!
[BULMA sobs]
[BULMA] I-I don't
know where he is...
They left me here...
I'm all alone!
[BULMA wails]
Uhh... What the heck
are you smiling about?
You do understand that I'm
about to kill you, don't you?
Don't be
so sure.
You won't even
lay a hand on me!
[RECOOME laughs]
Oh, boy!
That's a good one!
Hear that?! He says I
won't even lay a hand on him!
Guess I'll have to pound
him with my feet instead!
[BOTH chuckle]
What? Is he... Is he
trying to bluff 'em?
I hope not. He's gotta know
these guys won't back down.
I dunno... I don't think
Dad would say something
unless he thought he
could back it up.
[VEGETA] No... Impossible.
I... don't believe it!
Is Kakarot...
a Super Saiyan?!
But he's just a
low-class warrior!
It doesn't
make any sense!
Okay, enough with
the comedy routine...
Whadda ya' say we
get down to business?
Hands, feet, whatever.
It won't matter.
You're still
gonna die.
No, the last Super Saiyan
supposedly existed
over a thousand
years ago!
But, that was nothing
more than a legend!
I never actually
believed it to be true!
Even so... There's
no way a low-class
like Kakarot
could achieve it!
According to legend,
the last Super Saiyan
could only maintain his status
in the transformed state!
His power was
extraordinary...
he had no equal
in the universe!
But he was too
primitive to control it!
His rage burned
so intensely
that it eventually
consumed him.
And in the end, he was
destroyed by his own power!
[VEGETA] But if there were a
way to achieve such power,
I should know it! I am the
Prince of all Saiyans!
If there is to be a new Super
Saiyan, it should be me!
Prepare to
be scared...
Now feel the power!
Recoome! Yeah!
Die!
[RECOOME shouts]
[BOTH whimper]
Oh... Uh... Uh?
Uhhh...
[BOTH] Huh?
[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku's gone!
[GOHAN] What? What happened?
Did you see where he went?
No... Did you?
[GOHAN] No...
[RECOOME] Uhhh... Hey...
Wow. Jeice... This guy
is fast! Where'd he go?
Hmm... What the--!
[BOTH gasp]
[BURTER]
How did you...?!
[JEICE] What are you
tryin' to pull?!
What's goin' on?!
[BOTH gasp]
So there he is! Wow!
[thinking] Vegeta spotted
him before the rest of us.
He knew where Goku
was the whole time...
Man, I don't wanna know how
powerful that guy's getting...
You guys have caused
enough problems here.
It's time for
you to leave.
[BOTH growl]
Go back to your ships
and get off this planet.
Otherwise
you'll face me.
[BURTER &amp; JEICE yelling]
Who... is this guy?!
[RECOOME] Ooh, you
cocky little punk.
That's enough
showin' off.
We get the idea.
You're pretty quick.
Heh...
Yeah...
Except speed alone
isn't gonna be
enough to save you.
[RECOOME] See, I've got
this special little move
I like to use...
And trust me, you won't be able
to dodge this one. No, sir.
I'm gonna wipe out
this whole place!
Everything you see
is gonna be rubble!
Just one shot, and
you're all dead!
[thinking] Kakarot... Now we'll
see if I'm right about you!
[RECOOME] I hope you're
ready, Chief...
'Cause I'm about to send
all you little wimps
straight to hell!
[RECOOME growling]
[RECOOME laughs]
Dodge this, punk!
[RECOOME growling]
[KRILLIN] W-whoa! Look out!
Here it comes!
[RECOOME growls]
Now, full power!
Eraser Gun!
[RECOOME grunts]
[VEGETA gasps]
[RECOOME sputtering]
Sorry! I saw an opening
that seemed to scream out:
Attack!
So... I did.
[GOKU laughs]
[RECOOME grunting]
[GOHAN] I-Is that it?
Did Dad win?
Yeah... One punch!
That's crazy!
I just don't see
how it's possible!
It's like we're
in a dream!
The Goku we
left on Earth
couldn't be doing
this right now!
[thinking] But this isn't
the Goku we left on Earth...
Why is Recoome
still down?
Looks like he
barely touched him!
That attack didn't even
register on the scouters!
Damn! Kakarot...
The others may not have seen
the power behind that attack...
But you do not
deceive my eyes!
[VEGETA thinking]
With that one blow,
Kakarot has proved
himself stronger
than any Saiyan I
have ever known...
Perhaps any Saiyan
in a thousand years!
And I, the Prince
of all Saiyans,
have somehow become
this pauper's witness!
I'm the only one who
understands what he's become.
Even better than he
understands it himself!
Kakarot has become
a Super Saiyan!
[NARRATOR] What is this
Super Saiyan,
that even the mighty
Vegeta fears it?
And has Goku truly achieved
this legendary status?
Don't miss the
next Dragon Ball Z!