[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
it was the war between the Buus
as Majin Buu had to battle
his evil counterpart
whom he had expelled
from his very being!
Buu make you chocolate!
[NARRATOR] Lacking the
brute force needed to win,
Buu tried an
unconventional attack,
only to have it
backfire on him!
[NARRATOR] Buu had turned good,
but now he was good to eat!
And in the end,
he became a tasty treat.
But this was no
ordinary candy bar!
After eating it,
the bad Buu had a
violent change to undergo!
[NARRATOR]
To Mr. Satan's dismay,
the friend that he had
come to know was gone,
and a new Majin Buu was born!
I don't believe it!
Look at him!
He's even meaner
looking than the last one!
[screams]
[NARRATOR] With the newfound
ability to sense energy signals,
Majin Buu headed
directly for the Lookout!
He's here!
[gasping]
Look! Don't attack unless he
attacks one of us first! Got it?
Huh?
[NARRATOR]
Look out, everyone!
Majin Buu is
crashing the party!
[NARRATOR] And with Goten
and Trunks sound asleep,
and Gohan tied up in
the power raising ceremony,
it looks like the new Buu
is going to have his way
with the people of the Earth!
What demented plans does he
have in mind? Stay tuned!
[laughs]
I liked the first one better!
What happened?
Well he transformed! Obviously!
I found you, finally.
Incredible!
[PICCOLO]
Dude, don't encourage him.
Please.
Produce!
PRODUCE!!!
[YAMCHA] What's he talking
about? Produce? Produce what?
[KRILLIN]
I don't know! Ask him!
[YAMCHA]
Are you crazy? You ask him!
[KRILLIN] You're the
one that wants to know!
Hmm?
What?! What is it?
What is it that you
want us to produce? Tell us!
I was promised a good fight!
Produce the challenger!
Which one of you is it?
Don't be shy! Come forward!
The time has arrived!
Are you the one?
Me? No way! I would have
remembered a promise like that!
Yamcha! Was it you?
[YAMCHA]
Me? Are you nuts?!
[BULMA]
What's going on?
[CHICHI]
Where are they?
And what's all
the commotion about?
Oh, no!
He's here! He found us!
The one who made the promise.
He isn't here right now.
Where is he? The liar!
And I promise...
Give them two days
and they'll be ready.
There's no need for you
to destroy West City
or anything else.
I'm asking, have some patience.
They'll come to you.
They want to fight you.
[BUU]
Hmm... Are they really strong?
They are... unbelievably
strong! Wait and see.
[laughs]
Produce!
He's not here!
All right! He's here but
he can't fight right now!
Please! He's taking a nap!
Oh, well, wake him up!
But he just went to sleep!
Let him rest a little more!
I beg you!
Look! Buu!
He could fight you, but
wouldn't you rather fight him
when he's at his maximum power?
You want a real
challenge, don't you?
Waiting's no fun!
I hate to wait!
[PICCOLO] But the promise
made was for two days!
We still have one!
Well, that's true!
But I'm here now! Produce!
[BULMA]
He's here to fight Gotenks!
Gosh! I don't know if we
should let the boys
fight a monster like that!
[CHICHI] Uh, unh! No way!
He's not touching my son!
I'll fight him myself! Ha!
I'm not afraid
of that big bully!
ChiChi, darling,
I can't let you do this!
Let Piccolo handle it, okay?
Let go of me, Dad!
Right now! Let go!
I'm not scared of that fiend!
Let me go right now!
If he wants a fight,
I'll give him a fight!
Do it now! Produce!
[PICCOLO thinking] Trunks and
Goten--no, they're not ready!
I have to buy more time--at
any cost! It's our only chance!
Last time! Produce!
Please! Just one more day!
He'll be at his best tomorrow!
I promise!
Think about it!
This might be the
only chance you have
to test your true strength!
There's still
plenty of people on Earth
that you could kill
for your amusement
while you're waiting
for this fight!
Huh?
Uh, what? Piccolo!
[PICCOLO]
Be quiet, Dende!
Forgive me! But I know that
they can be wished back
with the Dragon Balls!
Hmm?
Now what?
[PICCOLO thinking]
I know what you're doing!
You're assessing how many
people are still alive!
Does this mean he's going
to give us the extra day?
Surely it would
take him that long
to hunt down
all of those people!
No. This is it!
We have got to act now!
[BULMA]
What's he doing?
[VIDEL]
I don't know.
Just taking a stroll!
He's got some nerve! Jerk!
[PICCOLO]
Krillin! Listen carefully!
I want you to go
wake up Trunks and Goten!
Keep them quiet!
Take them into the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber! To train!
Why don't they
just fight him now?
Are you crazy? There's no way!
He would annihilate Gotenks!
We've never encountered
anything like this guy!
[PICCOLO] No. No,
we need something more!
Trunks and Goten have
got to break through!
Krillin, this is
our last chance! Go!
Go while he's
looking the other way!
Dad! Let go! I demand that
you let go of me right now!
ChiChi! Would you stop that?
Please, don't go!
[CHICHI] It's time
to kick some butt!
[BULMA]
No!
Hey! That's your broom!
Come on! Let's go!
Ahh?!
[OX-KING]
ChiChi! Are you okay?
No, I'm not! I don't want
my son fighting that monster!
[sobs]
Look at him! Disgusting!
Makes my skin crawl.
[wails]
I'm scared, Mommy!
Snap out of it!
It's time to get up!
Come on, Goten! Get up!
Yeah! I love fried chicken!
Aye yi, yi! You're just
like your Dad, kid!
Goten! Wake up!
What is he doing?
Who knows? He's very peculiar!
[PICCOLO]
Huh?
[SUPER BUU]
Time to kill!
[gasps]
[PICCOLO] Stay still,
everyone! Don't move!
Whoa! Crazy!
Look! Wow!
[MAN]
Cool! Check it out! Fireworks!
[screaming]
Kai what's wrong?
Is it... Uh, oh!
Yes! The Earth! It's terrible!
Huh?
[SUPREME KAI] He's attacking
the entire populace!
[GOHAN thinking]
Is he for real?
Look, boy! They're everywhere!
Tien!
[TIEN]
Chiaotzu!
What have I done?!
I won't fail you!
I'll wish you all back!
Human Extinction Attack!
How do you like it?
Now, where is the strong one?!
I see! Yes! We just need a
short time to prepare him!
Yes! He can be ready in
one hour if that's okay!
Please, Buu!
What's an hour?
How long is it?
[PICCOLO] When all the sand
has fallen to the bottom,
one hour will be up!
No way!
Why not? What's an hour?
It's no big deal!
Unless you're scared!
Is that it, Buu?
Loud mouth girl!
You should die!
Wait! That girl is
Mr. Satan's daughter!
Hmm?!
One hour! She's asking!
Mr. Satan's girl! Not us! Her!
It's true!
Her scent--it's like his!
Very well! This Majin
Buu will wait one hour!
Then I will kill you all!
Mhmm.
[VIDEL]
How does he know my father?
Wow! That was close!
There must have been millions
of those blasts! How awful!
[whimpers]
[MR. SATAN] Come 'ere! Don't be
scared! I'll protect you, boy!
[snoring]
Hey! Come on, you guys!
We have to go to the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber to train!
Now!
[OLD KAI cackles]
Aliens? What? You're
kidding me! This is great!
Kai! I can't sense the Earth!
Yes! True! They're gone!
They've all been killed!
What? All of them?
But they were there when
I looked five minutes ago!
Right! Buu eliminated them
all with a single attack.
There were millions
of them, Goku!
Excuse me, Sir!
Hmm?
Time should be up!
We've been sitting here
for over twenty hours!
Oh, yes! I think you're right!
It should be over by now!
Amazing that it's not!
Whoo! You must be super strong!
Sometimes it takes
a little longer
for the really
strong ones, of course!
I'm tired of your games, Kai!
Do you realize
what you've done?
How much time we...
It worked! Huh?
Amazing! Was that
power really mine? Wow!
Sorry, I yelled at you!
You're not done yet!
Sit back down on the
ground so we can finish up!
[GOHAN] Right! I'm sorry
I ever doubted you sir.
[OLD KAI]
Sshh! Quiet!
[GOHAN]
Sorry!
[OLD KAI]
The aliens! Hehehehehe!
[SUPREME KAI]
Very impressive.
Incredible! I really didn't
think that he could pull it off!
I knew! He's a Kai!
My great ancestor!
He's brilliant! And shameless!
What do you mean shameless?
He was telling the truth
the whole time, Supreme Kai!
I mean the kiss.
Oh, yeah! That's right!
And now we're going to have to
deliver! I hope Bulma agrees!
Aw! Sure! She will!
It's to save the world!
[ROSHI] Look at him.
He's just sitting
there like a statue.
He's not even blinking.
[ANDROID 18]
He's so creepy.
[YAMCHA]
Well, if he thinks staring at it
is gonna make it go away
faster, he's mistaken.
I've tried it before.
[yawns]
[KRILLIN] Hey! Quiet, you guys!
He's right out there!
[GOTEN]
Where?
[KRILLIN]
Will you two be quiet?!
[NARRATOR] After experiencing a
sample of his awakened powers,
Gohan has new faith
in Old Kai's abilities!
[NARRATOR] But with
less than an hour to go
before Majin Buu
attacks Gotenks
and the few remaining
survivors on Earth,
will the power raising
be completed in time?
And will it be enough to defeat
this radically powerful enemy?
[NARRATOR] Stay tuned for more
excitement on Dragon Ball Z.