[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Z!
The struggle
against the Saiyans
took a
devastating turn,
as Yamcha was bested
by the evil Saibamen.
And the horror
only intensified
as the Saiyans
themselves entered the fray!
In a desperate attempt to save
Tien from the rampaging Nappa,
Chiaotzu made the
ultimate sacrifice.
[NARRATOR] Tien would
not let his friend's
final effort be in vain.
Tien channeled all
of his rage and fury
into a powerful energy
blast aimed at Nappa.
But it was no use.
Having spent the last of
his strength in the attack,
Tien collapsed while the
Saiyan remained standing.
No... I failed...
[NARRATOR] And though things
looked increasingly bleak
for our heroes,
a glimmer of hope remained!
Goku completed his
journey down Snake Way
and was transported
back to Earth by Kami,
where he quickly raced
to aid his friends!
But even with
all his speed,
Goku is still miles away
from the battlefield.
Can he get there before
more of his friends succumb
to the Saiyans?
Find out... Today!
Where's Kakarot?!
Where's that pitiful
excuse for a Saiyan hiding?!
[VEGETA]
What a coward...
Don't you say that about
my Dad! He's not a coward!
Come on...
Goku, where are you? Hurry!
Hang in there, guys!
I'm coming!
Faster, Nimbus!
Faster!
Until Goku arrives, it'll
be up to the three of us
to slow these
guys down...
Krillin, are you ready to
put this plan into action?
You bet! First, I distract him
by getting his attention.
[PICCOLO]
That's right, Krillin.
Then I'll come at him from
behind and grab his tail,
the Saiyan's
weak spot...
With any luck, he'll be
completely immobilized.
Then I attack him head
on and finish him!
All right, then...
Let's do this!
Heh!
Aah, secrets, secrets...
[NAPPA] What're you fools
whispering about over there?
That's for us to know, but
you'll find out soon enough...
[NAPPA] Sounds interesting...
Well, don't keep me
waiting too long.
The suspense
might kill me!
[NAPPA laughing]
Oh, sorry.
Guess I shouldn't get
your hopes up like that.
Not that you had any to
begin with. Hope, I mean.
It doesn't really
matter what you do.
You're still
gonna die!
Fiend!
Take this!
Yaahh!
Oh! I'm terrified!
Should I run away?
[KRILLIN shouting]
[thinking] That's it,
Krillin, keep him busy...
Hyaagh!
Huh?!
[thinking] Now!
Hn?
Hey! What the--?
Gohan!
[GOHAN screaming]
It worked!
[GOHAN continues screaming]
[NAPPA chuckling]
Give me a break...
Hyaah!
[GOHAN shouting]
[VEGETA chuckling]
[PICCOLO sputtering]
Wah, Piccolo!
[GOHAN whimpering]
[NAPPA] What's wrong, Namek?
[NAPPA laughing]
You look surprised!
Oh, now don't die on
me just yet...
You've still gotta tell
us about the Dragon Balls!
[KRILLIN] What happened?
What went wrong?
Piccolo had his tail!
Ha, ha, ha! Grab his tail!
That was your big plan?
Nappa and I have
evolved far beyond
that ridiculous
little weakness!
Good for us,
very bad for you!
One hit, and he's
supposed to be
one of the strongest
on this planet!
Piccolo?
Wake up!
Please, say something!
Piccolo, we need you!
Is he... Is he?
That's that...
Guess I'll have to find
someone else to play with
until he wakes up...
Hmm... How about you, kid?
[GOHAN whimpering]
Hmm. You know, you should
be proud. You're a Saiyan, too.
Well, I suppose you're
only half-Saiyan.
But still, that's
pretty good.
The Saiyans are the strongest
race in the galaxy...
[GOHAN whimpering]
Yep. Someday, you could've
been a mighty warrior...
Someday, but
not today...
[NAPPA laughing]
[GOHAN whimpering]
[ROSHI] Eh! There goes
the picture again...
[BULMA] Oolong, do
something! Fix it!
Come on, you
piece of junk!
We wanna see what's
going on out there!
No use...
[OOLONG] What do
you mean by that?
They've stopped
broadcasting,
which means that something
has gone horribly wrong...
[OOLONG laughing]
Horribly wrong, huh?
Well, that's just great!
We're all gonna die!
Can it, pork rind! How
dare you give up on them?!
Huh?
[ROSHI] Hey! What's that
sound? Where's it coming from?
Uh, ChiChi, why are you...
Where did you get those guns?
Launch left
them behind...
I just can't stand it!
I'm going to rescue Gohan!
No, ChiChi, please!
Stop and think about this!
I'm tired of thinking!
It's time for action!
[OX KING] I'm begging you,
Chichi! Don't leave like this!
[CHICHI] I have to protect
him! He needs me!
[OX KING]Calm down!
Get a hold of yourself!
[CHICHI] No! I'm going!
[OX KING] Well, if you
won't, then I will!
What? Put-me-down-right-now!
I've got to help Gohan!
--[CHICHI] He needs his mother!
--[OX KING] You're only going to
--[OX KING] get in the way!
--[CHICHI] Let go of me!
[CHICHI] If anything happened to
him, I'd never forgive myself!
[CHICHI] What kind of
grandfather are you?!
[CHICHI grunting]
[CHICHI] Doesn't anybody
care? Let me go!
[BULMA thinking]
Just look at us.
It's hard to believe
how happy we were then...
Tien... Yamcha... And my
little Goku, all grown up.
[BULMA thinking] I know
you're out there somewhere...
And I know that
no matter what,
you will always be
here to save us...
Hah! Aw, now don't tell
me you've had enough!
Show me your
Saiyan pride!
[GOHAN whimpering]
[GOHAN panting]
[thinking] I don't
know how much more
of this guy I can take...
Dad, where are you?
Ha ha ha! That's it!
Die like a man!
Hyaah!
[VEGETA laughing]
He's making you
look bad, Nappa!
Not for long...
He's mine!
[NAPPA growling]
Well, I guess
it's now or never...
[KRILLIN yelling]
[NAPPA yelling]
[KRILLIN grunting]
Hnn?!
[GOHAN whimpering]
[thinking] Time to see if all
that training paid off...
Here! Catch!
Destructo Disk!
Play catch, huh?
Why not!
Nappa! Don't touch it!
What a fool! That shot
would have sliced him in two!
So... close!
You! You cut me!
Oh, you've gone
and done it now!
You've scarred my
beautiful face!
And you're
gonna pay for it!
Here, little man!
Catch this one!
Hyaah!
[KRILLIN grunting]
Ah! Krillin! No!
[NAPPA laughing]
Sorry!
You lose!
[NAPPA shouting]
What in the...
Who did that?
[NAPPA snarling]
You Namekian trash!
You think you can shoot me in
the back and get away with it?
How dare you!!
[PICCOLO] I thought
it was your face...
Oh! Why you...
I'm gonna...
[VEGETA laughing]
I don't know Nappa, it's
an easy enough mistake.
Bring it on! I'm tired of
you and your loud mouth!
[NAPPA]
You arrogant fool!
Your life is mine to
take, whenever I want!
The only reason you're
still breathing
is because we need you to
tell us about the Dragon Balls.
And once we have that, you'll
be nothing more than a memory!
You caught me by surprise.
It won't happen again!
What in the world
am I sensing?
There's an incredibly
huge power level
that's heading
straight for us!
It's... It's my Dad!
He's different somehow,
but I know
it's him!
I knew he'd save
us... Get 'em, Goku...
Bah! You're just
trying to distract me!
You can't sense power levels
without some sort of device...
Afraid you're
wrong.
You're
bluffing!
Oh? Wait and see.
[thinking] Goku, they can't
hold out much longer!
You've got to hurry!
It's Goku,
all right!
He's on his way
here right now!
And judging by the
power I'm sensing,
you Saiyans are in store for
the fight of your lives!
Wow! This is great!
I knew my Dad would make it
here in time! Hurry up, Daddy!
Yes. I love it!
You're all a bunch of
liars! Where is he?
I don't see
anyone! Vegeta!
Whadda you think? Is Kakarot
really coming or not?
Calm down, Nappa! Certainly,
there's nothing to worry about!
Who cares anyway?
Let him come!
I feel two huge
power levels...
Two weaker ones...
One fading...
That only makes five. Something
terrible is happening!
Haah! Go, Nimbus! Hurry!
[NAPPA] Vegeta!
Hey, Vegeta!
Snap out of it!
You look like you've
seen a ghost or something!
[NAPPA laughing]
Come on! Don't tell me
there some sort of truth
to what these
fools are saying!
Something is definitely
headed this way.
But it can't
be Kakarot.
The power level's
too high...
Whatever is coming has a
power level of five-thousand.
What?! No way!
Five thousand?!
[VEGETA thinking] There's no
way that could be Kakarot!
How could he have
become so powerful?
Well, whatever it is, I have
to be prepared for anything.
The people of this
planet have ways
of hiding their
true power levels.
Five thousand could just
be the beginning.
It can't be! Your scouter
must be malfunctioning!
[PICCOLO laughing]
[PICCOLO] So then, you
still think I'm bluffing?
Nappa! Quickly!
Kill them all!
We can't let them join
with this fighter!
If it is Kakarot,
he has to know
that we will not be
opposed by anyone!
Huh?!
Uwaah!
[KRILLIN growling]
[NAPPA] But... what
about the Dragon Balls?
[VEGETA] We don't need
these fools to find them!
It's all becoming
clear to me now!
It must have
been the Nameks
who created the Dragon Balls
here on this planet...
I've heard of the Magic
Balls of Namek before,
but I'd always thought
they were just a legend!
It can't just be a coincidence
that while searching
for these Dragon Balls,
we find a Namek!
I get it!
A Namekian is all we need
to make the Dragon Balls,
and Planet Namek is
loaded with them!
And if this one doesn't
want to cooperate,
we can always find another
Namekian that will!
So you're...
expendable!
Hey! Piccolo!
Leave now!
I can take care of
this bully by myself
until my Dad
gets here!
What?
If we lose you, then the
Dragon Balls will disappear
and we won't be
able to wish
any of our friends
back to life!
Thanks for your
concern, Gohan,
but I really don't think you
can handle these guys alone...
Just for that...
you go first.
I need to
help them...
But how? I can barely
move... Piccolo... Gohan!
[GOHAN growling]
Okay, brat!
You die!
Raahh!
[GOHAN whimpering]
Raagh!
Haah!
Hnn?!
[PICCOLO]
I don't believe it...
Uh, Gohan...
Was... was that you?
[NAPPA snarling]
You!
I'll kill you!
[NAPPA screaming]
[NAPPA growling]
[GOHAN whimpering]
Oh, no...
It's time...
[NAPPA growling]
[GOHAN whimpering]
[NAPPA shouting]
[GOHAN wailing]
[KRILLIN groaning]
Where am I?
Where's my dad?
This is... sour...
[GOHAN chuckling]
[PICCOLO thinking] Gohan!
No! No!
Until now, training
you was out of vengence,
making you worthy enough
to be my opponent.
But... something's changed...
No matter what happens
to you, Gohan,
I will always be
there to protect you.
[NAPPA yelling]
[GOHAN screaming]
[PICCOLO growling]
Hrgh!
[PICCOLO screaming]
[NARRATOR] Has Piccolo made the
ultimate sacrifice for Gohan
by throwing himself in the path
of Nappa's furious attack?
Will Goku arrive
in time
to save his remaining friends
from the diabolical Saiyans?
And even if he does,
what chance does he have
of saving the rest
of the planet?
Find out, on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!