[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan and Krillin successfully
summoned the Dragon
with the help of their
Namekian friend, Dende.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the enraged Frieza
was rushing to the scene
in his bid for immortality!
With danger approaching, will
they make their wishes in time?
Find out today!
Man, check him out!
I'm glad he's friendly!
At least, I hope he is!
Yeah, me too. He's... huge!
You who have awakened
me from my slumber.
I will grant you
any three wishes
that are within
my power to fulfill
as a boon for
summoning me.
[KRILLIN] Hey, alright! Oh, wow!
That's a heck of a deal, huh?
Three wishes instead of one!
Didn't I tell ya? Namek's
great! You can't beat it!
Yeah, no kidding!
Namek's awesome!
No, please guys! Don't
disrespect the Dragon!
Uh... okay. I know one!
Well, Vegeta's men killed
some friends of ours.
Could you please ask
Porunga to bring them back
to our dimension?
Yes, I can try it.
[DENDE speaking Namek]
Your wish is unacceptable.
Huh?!
Only one life can be restored
for each wish that you use.
What?! Oh no!
[KING KAI] Hmm...!
Darn! What a pity!
Seems that Gohan and
Krillin can only wish
three people back
to their dimension.
What? That's not gonna cut it!
I think he's right.
Let's see here...
Chiaotzu, Yamcha,
Piccolo, and me!
[YAMCHA] Just count
your eyes and add one!
What do you know?!
Well, I know this: I'm one
of the three going back! Huh?
Wait! No! You need to fix
your hair! You should stay!
[TIEN growls]
Fix my hair?! So I like
to comb my hair alot!
At least I have hair, Cue Ball!
Cue Ball, huh? You jerk!
[CHIAOTZU] Hey, guys!
Why don't we draw straws?
Yeah, right! There's
one small problem:
You and Tien are telepathic!
[CHIAOTZU] We're not
cheaters! How dare you!
[ALL growl]
I'm the one that needs to go!
That's right! I need to
talk to Gohan right now!
What?!
Please, sir!
Look! I'm enjoying the fresh
air, but I don't have all day.
If you can't make up your mind,
just wish for "nothing"
three times so I can go.
Wow. A Dragon with
a sense of humor.
[DENDE] Krillin,
we need to hurry!
Frieza could be on his way!
He's right! There's no time
to stew over this, Gohan!
We have to make
up our minds!
Uhh... So one stays,
but which one?
Man! It's gonna be a tough
call any way you slice it.
I understand that you'd
like to talk to Gohan now.
But, that wouldn't be
fair to the others!
You're darn right!
Let me talk to Gohan!
I've known his father
since he was just a kid
so let me tell him what to do!
You can forget that!
Yeah, that's not fair!
I get it! I know what
the deal is now.
You saved Gohan's life and now
it's payback time! Of course!
That's not it! Trust me, please.
Alright, I will. You're the only
one not acting like a rabid dog.
Thanks.
Gohan, can you hear me?
It's me, Piccolo!
[KING KAI] You don't have
to yell, you know!
[PICCOLO] Oh, sorry. Gohan?
Huh?
[PICCOLO] It's me, Piccolo!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Piccolo!
[PICCOLO] Listen
carefully, Gohan!
Uh... Where is he?
I can hear you,
but I can't see you!
[PICCOLO] I know! King Kai
opened up a direct
telepathic link
between the two of us!
And just ten cents
a minute! That's my rate!
Hey, I still got it!
Hee, hee, hee!
Huh? What?
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN] Piccolo?
Are you still there?
[PICCOLO] Yes, Gohan, I know
you don't have much time
so I'll get straight
to the point.
Gohan, use your first wish to
wish me back to your dimension!
Uh-uh!
Hey, no way, Piccolo!
That's not fair!
Be quiet!
Huh?
[CHIAOTZU] Whoa...
Better! Now Gohan listen up!
Wish me back there first!
Huh?
If I come back, then Kami
will return to Earth as well!
And so will the Dragon Balls!
You know what that means.
Hey! He's right! Then we'll
have plenty of wishes!
To bring the others
back... That's brilliant.
Yeah, you got it.
What a great idea!
Man, you're the bomb!
You rock, Piccolo!
Alright! And now,
for the second wish.
[ALL] Hm?
[PICCOLO] Gohan, after you wish
me back to your dimension,
I'd like you to wish me
over to the planet Namek.
That's where I belong!
It's my people that Frieza
destroyed! It's my fight!
He needs to pay for what he's
done and I intend to make him.
Hey, you promised
never to fight Frieza!
[KING KAI yells]
I know how much you
care about me, old man!
But I've got to do
what I've got to do!
Gohan! Are you clear
on the first two wishes?
Yes! Crystal clear, Piccolo!
That a boy! I guess I'll be
seeing you real soon then!
Yeah! We'll be fighting side by
side again! Just like on Earth!
[KING KAI whimpers]
Hey! What's the deal?! Piccolo!
I see! Now, I get it!
Bad boy!
You get what you want
from my training and then
tell me to take a hike!
Heh, well, to be blunt,
yeah. That's right.
What?! You brat! Ah!
[PICCOLO] So this is it. This is
what it's like to have a mom.
[KING KAI growls]
That does it!
[TIEN] Whoa! Easy does it!
Down, big guy!
[TIEN] King Kai!
Settle down! Please!
We can't let you go
until you calm down!
[KING KAI yells]
[PICCOLO] It's time!
Time? Time to get annhilated!
Time to get blown away!
You have no idea what you're
getting yourself into!
[KRILLIN] Alright. Well,
what do you think, Gohan?
Should we follow
Piccolo's plan or not?
Yeah!
[KRILLIN] Dende!
Yes, what?
For the first wish, could
you please ask the Dragon
to bring our friend Piccolo
back to this dimension!
Right! B-Bring Piccolo back.
I think I can do that.
[GOHAN] Well, this is it.
This is the whole
reason we came here!
Huh! Something's
on the way here now!
It's Frieza!
I know it! It has to be!
No! Agh...!
[VEGETA] Come on, Kakarot!
Darn it! Hurry!
You're no good to me until your
strength is fully restored!
Rats! This isn't good!
Ah! What?!
Darn it! How could I
have slept that long?!
It's-It's dark out!
Wait a second! It's not night
time! The horizon isn't dark!
What in the world is going on?!
Oh, no... Oh, no, no!
Darn it! I should have never
trusted those Earthlings!
Hurry up, Kakarot!
[DENDE speaking in Namek]
Alright. It shall
be done. As you wish.
[VEGETA] How could
I be so foolish!
Those little punks
are gonna pay for this!
[VEGETA] Darn it! Where are
they? Where are they?!
Oh, come on! They have to
be around here somewhere!
Huh?!
Look at
that thing!
Th-They summoned him! The
Earthlings have tried to summon
the Dragon of Legend without me!
Alright! I am not going to
let this shake my composure!
Damn it!
[VEGETA] And to top it off,
Frieza should be arriving
any minute now!
They're at my ship! How dare
they try to outsmart me?!
Hey! Cool! You're alive!
Yes...
You did it, Gohan!
Now! Wish me there!
Come on! Do it!
Go! I don't care! Your
generation just can't be taught!
[KING KAI screams]
[MR. POPO hums]
[MR. POPO laughs]
A butterfly!
And at this altitude!
[MR. POPO laughs]
[MR. POPO gasps]
[MR. POPO] It's... It's the
ghost of Kami! Oh, no!
Are... Are you... Are you real?!
Indeed. Thanks for
watering the plants
while I was gone, Mr. Popo.
Popo? What's wrong?
You look pale, my friend.
Oh, Kami! You're too much.
I... I missed you!
I am running out of patience!
Speak, now! Tell me
your next wish, now!
Quick! Dende, tell him that
we'd like our friend Piccolo
brought here to the planet Namek
from wherever he is right now!
That's our next wish!
Okay, yes! Got it!
Huh?!
Hey, guys! He's awake!
And I bet he got up on the
wrong side of the bed!
[DENDE speaks in Namek]
I will grant this wish.
The one you call Piccolo will
be brought to Namek now.
[GOHAN chuckles]
[CHIAOTZU] Hey.
There he goes. Wow!
Fool! He could get hurt.
[PORUNGA] Your second
wish has been granted.
Now, speak. Tell
me your last wish.
Say what? But I don't
see him! Do you?
No! I don't!
Hey, sir! We...
[DENDE] Guys, please! If Porunga
says he's here, he's here!
We're the ones who messed up!
He could be anywhere
on the planet!
What? Oh, no!
But we could use
our last wish
to wish him to
this exact spot.
[DENDE screams]
[VEGETA growls]
Vegeta!
What's the matter? You two
look a little surprised
to see me.
[GOHAN] Well, nothing really.
Everything's fine!
[VEGETA] No, I don't
think everything is fine.
[VEGETA] And I will tell you
why everything is NOT fine.
Because you two... You
summoned the Dragon, didn't you?
Shame on you! How dare you?
I spoiled you with new suits,
took you in, saved your lives,
all of that! And this
is how you repay me?
Well, you can kiss
each other goodbye!
Hold on a second!
You only wanted to use
one wish for yourself, right?
Well, we've only used
two of our wishes,
and there's
still one left!
[KRILLIN] Gohan! Why did
you have to tell him that?!
[VEGETA] Thank you!
Huh?
[VEGETA chuckles]
I'm glad you're not as
smart as I thought you were!
[VEGETA laughs]
[FRIEZA growls]
Huh? What in the world
is that bizarre apparition?!
Four of them are
gathered beneath it.
No, it can't be! Why those
scurvy, low-life opportunists!
How could they?!
Speak! Make your last wish now.
[VEGETA] Alright, kid!
We're out of time!
Ask him to grant
me eternal life!
Now!
Come on!
Come here, you
little green bean!
You need a little
encouragement, huh?!
Hey!
[VEGETA] Hurry up, kid!
[DENDE] Let go! Please stop!
Look: Do or die, we need
to stop this, now!
Well, it seems to
make sense, but, well...
Frieza's on the way
and my dad still needs
more time to recover!
So this is it, huh?
Namek, my home...
[PICCOLO] This is what I've
yearned for my whole life,
without ever
knowing it was here...
No! No time! I have
to stay focused.
Let's see here...
Gohan, where are you?
[PICCOLO] No...
Not there either...
They're not even close! I guess
the Dragon had bad aim! Huh?!
[PICCOLO] I've never felt a
power like this one!
But it's dark!
Man! He's stronger than
I imagined he would be!
[PICCOLO growls]
Ah, well, what the heck.
Shoot, you only live once.
[PICCOLO chuckles]
Well, looks like
I'm back in action!
[DENDE] I'm sorry, sir! I can't!
Make your last wish now!
[PORUNGA growls]
You heard him, make the darn
wish! What's the matter?!
Don't tell me you'd rather
be destroyed by Frieza?
Don't you get it? I'm the
only one who can stop him!
[KRILLIN] I can't take
much more of this...
[GOHAN] Uh, oh! Hey!
We're out of time!
Frieza's close! I can feel it!
Desperate times call
for desperate measures!
Hm?
Dende! Do whatever
Vegeta tells you! Now!
[BOTH] Huh?!
[KRILLIN] We're definitely
all going to be wiped out
if we don't do
something fast!
Man! I hate this!
Damn! But I guess trusting
Vegeta is better
than dying, right?!
Yeah, I guess so...
[VEGETA laughs]
Kid, I like your style.
--[VEGETA] Hurry up!
--[DENDE screams]
[VEGETA] Do it, boy!
Make the wish!
[DENDE speaking in Namek]
[VEGETA] This is it!
It's really happening!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[DENDE speaking in Namek]
[VEGETA] Yes! A
new Vegeta is born!
An indestructable power
that only can get stronger
from every battle!
[DENDE speaking in Namek]
Vegeta!
[DENDE] Huh...?
What's going on?!
[DENDE screams]
[KRILLIN] Oh, man...
I don't belive it!
[GOHAN gasps]
[ALL gasping]
Hey! What's the deal!
I don't feel any different.
Is this supposed to happen?
Does this normally happen?!
Well, someone speak up!
Am I immortal or not?!
[DENDE] No, you're
not immortal...
Dende? Hey, are you alright?
What's the matter?
It's Guru... He's gone.
[gasping]
I'm sorry, Dende...
He was like a
grandfather to me...
Guru, I-I asked you not
to die while I was gone...
Wait a minute-- That's it?!
Hey! You mean that
when this guy kicks it,
the Dragon Balls are
completely useless?!
Yes. They're part of him.
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] Idiots!
So, I guess we're back to
where we started from!
I was about to kill you guys
for betraying me, wasn't I?
Yes, I remember now!
That was it!
[VEGETA growls]
Okay, who's fir--
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA whimpers]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
So, you are the ones? Naughty!
I don't see how three
shrimps and a burnt-out Saiyan
managed to defeat
the Ginyu Force.
But now it's your turn!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN whimper]
[DENDE &amp; VEGETA whimper]
Don't worry, it
won't hurt too bad.
Really, death is my specialty.
[NARRATOR] The dark hour
has finally arrived!
Is it lights out for
this unlikely foursome?
Or can Piccolo lend a hand?
Is his training with
King Kai enough?
Will Goku wake up in
time to help his friends
on the next Dragon Ball Z?