[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu was on the rampage.
But getting rid
of his better half
wasn't as easy as he thought.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Vegeta made a plea
to the people
of Earth for help.
[VEGETA] Raise your
hands up to the sky,
and offer a portion
of your energy,
we could use it to defeat
Majin Buu once and for all!
[YAMCHA]
Yeah!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[NARRATOR] But aside
from family and friends,
no one would comply
with his request.
Naa! Let's go see
a movie or something.
That was so weird!
No kidding!
[grunts]
Are they mad?
When are you going to grow up?!
Can't you Earthlings do
anything for yourselves?!
[NARRATOR] With the good Buu
being crushed under foot,
the opportunity to
form the Spirit Bomb
was rapidly slipping away.
Vegeta had no choice
but to try again.
[VEGETA] Hey!
People of the Earth!
Raise your hands up right now
or you're all going to die!
[NARRATOR] As humanity turns
its back on Vegeta's plea,
Goku's Spirit Bomb wastes away.
Can the Saiyans get
through to them in time?
[PORUNGA growls lowly]
[MOORI] Mmm!
What a grim situation.
The people of Earth
have closed their hearts.
[DENDE]
Yes, Elder.
For some reason they're
not listening to Vegeta!
Not one extra person
has offered their energy!
[KIBITO KAI]
Do you think Vegeta could
soften his request somewhat?
You know. Ask them nicely.
[OLD KAI] He could
if he wasn't a proud,
pigheaded, arrogant fool!
[KINITO KAI]
Look! He's trying again!
[VEGETA]
People of the Earth!
Please! I beg of you!
[ALL gasp]
[OLD KAI]
I'll be darned!
[VEGETA] You have to
listen to me!
Please! We're
running out of time!
[thinking]
Remarkable!
Come on! Work!
[VEGETA] Raise your hands!
Do it, before it's too late!
Don't let Majin Buu
destroy you
and your children!
Please! Don't let him win!
[MAN 1]
Maybe he's right.
[MAN 2] You mean you're
actually going to do it?
Yeah! Why not? What if
Buu still is alive?
Well, all right.
But I'm telling the guys
at the lodge there.
[MAN 1] Ah, tell 'em
what you want.
[MAN 2] Well now, do you
feel like an idiot?
Aaah...!
[panting]
Dang! I feel like
I just ran a mile!
You hoser!
No, sir! You ain't
getting' mine, aye!
I know what you are, aye!
You're a demon!
[WOMAN] Aah!
Put your hands down!
My son's dying! It's a trick!
[MAN 3]
What? Huh?
They stole his soul!
Don't raise your hands up!
They're trying
to steal our souls!
Idiots! Ugh!
They deserve to die!
[distant rumble]
[MR. SATAN]
Oh, no! Buu!
[chuckles]
[yells]
[KID BUU yells]
[BUU screams]
[KID BUU chuckles intensely]
He's finished! He doesn't
have anything left!
This isn't right!
My Buu can't die in my dream!
[coughing, whimpering]
--[KID BUU chuckles]
--[BUU groans]
[BUU screams]
[BUU groans]
[KID BUU]
Me Buu! Not you!
[laughs intensely]
[MR. SATAN]
Buu!
[VEGETA]
It's his finishing move!
No way! Not while
the champ is still alive!
[yelling]
[MR. SATAN grunts]
Wow! I hit him... in the head!
[MR. SATAN]
So uh...
y-y-you want some of this, huh?
Come on! Let's go! I dare ya!
Uh, oh!
[KID BUU grunting]
Marvelous! Now what?
[screams]
I'm going to buy
you some time, Kakarot!
But you're gonna
have to get through
to those nitwit Earthlings.
[GOKU] Vegeta!
You've been wished back!
Your body's not going
to be as durable this time.
So be careful.
[yells]
[laughs]
Fool! I'll rip
that arm right off!
[coughs]
[chuckles]
Ah! Vegeta!
Hey. Kakarot...
Any day now!
I can't believe those fools.
No! Fellow Earthlings!
Please! Listen!
We need your energy now!
Raise your hands up!
I beg of you!
There's no time left!
This is our last
chance to beat Majin Buu!
Hey Father. Who is that?
Well, I think you know.
The scar on my
chest reminds us.
It's Goku, our friend.
Who rescued me
from death itself.
There's no doubt.
[GOKU] Everyone! Please!
Raise your hands up!
Send me your energy now!
Ahh! Yes! You're right,
Father! It is him!
[BORA]
Do as he bids of us, Upa!
Raise your hands!
Everyone, raise your hands!
It's okay! Don't be afraid!
He's a very good man!
[YAJIROBE] So what's
the deal with this
raisin' hands stuff?
I'm not in school anymore.
[KORIN]
Fine, forget about it.
I'll just tell Goku
you didn't want to!
Look! It's up!
You'd better not say that.
[KORIN] You just sit
on your behind anyway.
Eh. You don't need energy.
[ANDROID 17]
It's been a long time
since I've heard that voice.
Hmm! Well, what do we have
here? Two more volunteers.
No way!
Yeah! I forgot
our anniversary!
[MAN 1]
Aw, man!
[BOTH yell]
Hey. You beat me to it.
[TIEN yells]
Here it is, my friend!
Take our energy!
Use it as you please!
Beat him, Goku! Show
him what true power is!
[GOKU]
Fellow citizens! Please!
Raise your hands!
We need more energy!
I think I know that voice.
It's Goku! Yeah!
Oh, my gosh! I think you're
right, Eighter. Here, Goku!
If it feels good, do it.
Yes. In this case,
you're right.
[VILLAGERS chuckling]
--[GIRL 1] Uh-huh. Yeah.
--[GIRL 2] Really. seriously.
[GIRL 2] They were at
the movies together.
[GIRL]
That guy sounded cool.
Aaah...!
[GOKU] Citizens, please!
The situation is critical!
Raise your hands!
[WOMAN 1]
Who's that guy?
He's different than
the last one.
[WOMAN 2] I don't know,
but I like this one.
I believe him.
[WOMAN 3] I think it's
scandalous. I mean, really.
Who are they to
talk to us from the sky?
[VEGETA groaning]
[KID BUU chuckles]
[snarls]
Ah!
Oh, no! That's all we
gained after all that? Ugh!
[KID BUU chuckles]
[yells]
Ah-haaa!
Oh, no! He's hurt!
[VEGETA groaning]
No way. I won't let it happen.
[VEGETA] No pink, mutant
freak is going to defeat me!
I'll beat you!
[grunts]
[KID BUU growls]
[yells]
Please! Hurry!
Offer up your energy!
Can't you understand?
If you don't help now
we're all going to die!
[GOHAN]
This is crazy!
Why isn't anybody
giving their energy?
I guess when you consider
everything that's
happened to them lately,
it's no wonder they're not
able to believe or understand.
Especially in
something they can't see.
[PICCOLO]
But...
sometimes when people
can't see the truth,
they need witnesses
to help build their faith.
[GOHAN]
What do you mean?
I mean they can't see Goku
or Vegeta but they can see us.
Let's split up and go
tell whoever will listen
to trust in the voice,
do you follow me?
Mm, hmm! Now I get it!
Excellent idea!
--Yeah!
--Uh, huh!
[PICCOLO]
Let's do it!
[GOHAN]
Yeah!
[GOTEN]
Ha-ha!
[KID humming]
Hello, there!
May I please have your
attention for a moment?!
[BRUNETTE GUY] So she like,
orders her steak rare...
[GOHAN] If we don't raise
our hands to the sky soon,
we're all gonna die!
[BRUNETTE LADY]
Get out! No way!
[BRUNETTE MAN]
What a freak!
Why won't they listen to me?
Huh? Whoa! Excuse me!
[GOHAN] Everyone! The voice
was telling the truth!
Please raise your hands to
the sky before it's too late!
[indistinct yelling,
car horns honking]
[thinking]
They won't listen!
[FARMER]
Ain't that somethin'!
Now that is an ear of corn!
[FAMER'S WIFE]
Yes, we've been blessed
with a good crop.
[TRUNKS]
Look out below!
[FARMER] They's skydivin'
without parachutes!
Hey! The guys that
are fighting Majin Buu
need us to raise
our hands to help.
Look! Kid! I'm busy here!
See! Now beat it!
No! It's true! Our dads
are the ones fighting him.
Hey. If you boys play over
there, I'll give you these.
[GOTEN]
Sure! I'll take one.
Thanks a lot! I love corn!
[MONTHER] Stay away
from my baby!
[gasps]
[MAN]
Monster!
[PEOPLE yelling]
[grunts]
[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA yelling]
[KID BUU yells]
[laughs]
Please! Time is almost up!
Don't any of you care
if you live or die? Hurry!
[MAN] So now we're
fools, is that it?
[WOMAN] Yeah, really! That's
no way to ask a favor!
Man! Forget that dude!
Why raise the hands?
Why not the feet?
I'm a foot guy!
Come on! Sheesh!
Just who does he
think he is, yelling at us?
I catch enough of that
stuff from my husband.
[LADY B]
No kidding!
[LADY C] Yeah! Where does he
get off telling us what to do?
Idiots! Don't they
have any brains?!
What's wrong
with you ingrates?!
Can't you lend
us a hand?! Come on!
How many times have
I saved you people? Huh?
[BOY] Hey!
That was Mr. Satan!
Mom! It's Mr. Satan!
I'd recognize
that voice anywhere!
Hey! You're right! Wow!
[GUY IN HAT] Oh no.
It was him all right!
Dude! If that was not the Champ,
I'll eat the hat I'm wearing!
I believe it was!
[MAN A]
It really is him!
[MAN B]
Mr. Satan!
[WOMAN A]
He saved us from Cell
and now he's trying to
save us from Majin Buu!
[MAN C] So he's the
mastermind behind this!
[MAN D] Who were
those other guys?
Uh. Huh?
[WOMAN B] Yeah! If that
was really the Champ,
why didn't he
talk to us sooner?
Please! Don't doubt!
I was working undercover.
That's why I
didn't speak to ya.
I was keeping
my identity a secret.
Now raise up those hands
and lend me that energy
so I can defeat
Majin Buu! Ha-ha!
Uh, yeah...
Uh, nothing personal!
I just don't think
they would do it
unless they thought it was me.
And at this point, defeating
Majin Buu is all that matters.
Everyone! It's him!
Mr. Satan!
Raise your hands!
It's him! The Champ!
[indistinct chatter, cheering]
[ADMIRAL] That's it,
men! Don't hold back!
Give everything you've got!
[SAILORS cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] Unbelievable!
Using his special powers,
the World Champion is
speaking to the entire planet
from a battle that we can't
even see! This is fantastic!
[CITIZENS]
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Hey! Wow!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot!
--[VEGETA chuckles]
--[KID BUU yells]
[VEGETA yells]
[CITIZENS]
Let's go Champ!
Beat Buu! Beat Buu! Beat Buu!
Go Champ! Go Champ!
[chanting continues]
[chuckles]
Go Champ! I don't believe
it. That guy, I swear.
[laughs]
[GOHAN]
This is amazing!
It's like every one's
giving they're energy now!
Yeah! Dad!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS cheer, giggle]
All right! Go Dad! Ha-ha!
[cheering, hollering]
[CITIZENS] Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
[chanting continues]
[cheering, hollering]
[cheer, laughing]
[KID BUU laughing]
[GOKU] Come on!
We're almost there.
Just a little bit longer.
Hang in there, Vegeta!
Hey! What's the big hold-up?
Don't tell me they're
still not giving their energy!
--[KID BUU yells]
--[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA gasps, groans]
No! It's all over!
[yells]
[GOKU thinking]
Wait...
[GOKU]
Here we go!
[gasps in awe]
[NARRATOR] At last,
thanks to Mr. Satan,
the long awaited energy has
finally arrived from Earth!
[KID BUU grunts]
[snarls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Here it comes, Vegeta!
Now! Move away!
[NARRATOR] With the
Spirit Bomb complete,
Goku is ready to
aim and fire! Stay tuned!