[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku found himself
in dire straights
as a radical virus
attacked his heart,
leaving him crippled with pain.
[GOKU] Gohan...
[GOKU grunts
[NARRATOR] Unable to respond
to Android 19's offensive,
the mighty Super Saiyan could
only lay lie there and watch
helplessly as the android
robbed him of his energy.
[GOKU grunts]
[NARRATOR] It was a theft that
would have proved fatal for Goku
if lightning hadn't struck
in the form of Vegeta.
[ANDROID 20] Huh?!
[NARRATOR] After his
dramatic entrance,
the Saiyan prince astonished
everyone by transforming
into a Super Saiyan right
before their very eyes.
[VEGETA] That's how I
became a Super Saiyan.
The sleeper has awakened!
I am the prince of
all Saiyans once again!
You may have become
a Super Saiyan,
but your new found powers
are still no match for us.
Please demonstrate, Android 19.
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[NARRATOR] For the Androids,
there's one Super Saiyan
down and only one to go.
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[ANDROID 19 growls]
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[GOHAN gasps]
[ANDROID 19] Haa-hoo-haaa!
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
Hmm... Just as I thought.
You're nothing!
Huh?!
Silly robot! Do you really
think you have a chance
against a Super
Saiyan like me?
Your brain must
be malfunctioning.
Fresh out of the factory
with no warranty...
And already broken.
What a pity...
[ANDROID 19 whimpers]
[VEGETA yells]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[ANDROID 19 screams]
[VEGETA grunts]
[BOTH gasp]
Man! Vegeta!
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
[ANDROID 19] Mal... function...
[VEGETA] My, my!
What do we have here?
[ANDROID 19] ...function...
Oh, yes! The ultimate
tub of lard bucket of bolts!
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
Huh?!
[ANDROID 19 yells]
[VEGETA] So, are you scared yet?
[ANDROID 19 whimpers]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA shouts]
[ANDROID 19 growls]
I think you have an oil leak.
What a bad deal!
Such a fragile unit!
[ANDROID 19 growls]
[VEGETA grunts]
[ANDROID 19 yells]
[gurgles]
[ALL gasp]
[PICCOLO] Let's get outta here!
[VEGETA] Despicable!
What a useless machine!
[ANDROID 19] Hmm?!
[ANDROID 19] Oh, yes!
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
I have you now!
And soon I will have
all of your energy!
[ANDROID 20 laughs]
[KRILLIN] Oh, no!
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[ANDROID 19] Do not
try to escape, yes!
It is useless.
Until I have your energy,
I will never let you go.
Never, huh? Let's see...
[VEGETA growls,
ANDROID 19 grunts]
[crunching]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] Well so far
I'm impressed!
You're very true
to your word!
But "never" can be
a long time, Android!
[thinking] C'mon, Goku!
Hang in there.
We're not going to
let you leave us again!
We're going to beat this thing!
[ANDROID 19 grunting,
crunching]
Something wrong?
You seem like you're
under a lot of pressure!
Still think that you can hang on
long enough to steal my energy?
[ANDROID 19] I will
never let you go!
Yes, that's the spirit, Android!
Never say die!
[VEGETA growls]
[ANDROID 19 wails]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[ANDROID 19 whimpers]
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
[GOHAN gasps]
[ANDROID 19 groans]
[VEGETA] Hm!
[VEGETA] So, these are the
devices that you androids use
to rob people of their energy.
[ANDROID 19 whimpers]
[VEGETA] What's the matter?
You're the one who
started this game!
And now you don't
want to play anymore?!
You were enjoying
yourself before
when you were sucking
the life out of Kakarot!
[ANDROID 19 whimpers]
So, I guess it's
true after all!
Androids do experience fear...
[ANDROID 19 whimpers, screams]
[ANDROID 20] Hmm? Huh?!
[ANDROID 19 whimpers]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Enough!
Don't be absurd!
It's enough because
you're losing!
You've come here to destroy us!
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
[VEGETA] Fool!
You're going to have to
finish what you started!
[VEGETA] Time has run
out for you, Android!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[TIEN gasps]
[GOHAN growls]
Man! What power!
Here it comes!
A little going away
present for you!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA yells]
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[TIEN gasps]
[ANDROID 19 screams]
[ANDROID 19 automated
sobs repeatedly]
[VEGETA] I only wish there
was a junkyard nearby
so we could give him
a proper burial!
VEGETA chuckles]
Wow... Goodness!
Would you look at
the size of that?
[YAJIROBE gasps]
My gosh! We don't want to
get caught in that smoke,
we'd better go in low!
Bulma, let's just get the
heck out of here, please!
You coward!
We're already there!
No! Turn around!
It's not too late!
[BULMA] Let go, you big oaf!
We're going and that's final!
-[YAJIROBE] We could get killed!
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
Now look what you've
done! You woke the baby!
--Big mouth!
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
--You scared him!
It's that big,
burly voice of yours!
[YAJIROBE] Say what?!
You're out of your mind!
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
[KRILLIN] Man! That
android's toast!
[PICCOLO] Yeah...
More like burnt toast...
[ANDROID 19] Mal...
function... Malfunctio...
[VEGETA] Hmm...
[ANDROID 20 growls]
You are a bit stronger
than I anticipated.
But it is nothing
I cannot handle.
Your defeat is imminent.
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] Yes, your friend
managed to steal quite a bit
of energy from me
before I stopped him!
Now's your chance to beat me!
A vicious attack now,
could be sufficient!
[thinking] How can
he be so confident?
What is he hiding?
[thinking] Yes!
He is shrewd!
He seems completely
at ease, but is he?
Let me ask you this:
What makes you think
that you are going to do
any better than him?
You're an android, too!
I bet your head rolls
just as well as his does!
Fool.
I am far superior to
the Android 19 model.
Stamping you out of existence
is a trifle for a unit like me.
You're bluffing, friend!
Let's se what you've got!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[VEGETA] Hm!
Oh, man!
There he goes!
Wow! He's running!
Hey, Baldy, hurry!
Throw me one of those beans!
[KRILLIN] Huh?!
Uh, hey!
Wait a sec!
Listen, you idiot!
He's going to get away!
[PICCOLO growls]
Krillin! Do it!
Whatever you say!
[KRILLIN] Heh!
I'll give him a small one!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[VEGETA] Ahh!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] I appreciate
the assistance
but you're not
needed here anymore.
You should go home
where it's safe!
You'll only get in my way!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN] Huh?!
[KRILLIN growls]
Well, good riddance!
Man, that guy is
the biggest jerk!
I have to agree with you,
but he's a genius when
it comes to fighting!
Vegeta was weakened
by the other Android.
He was vulnerable so
he bluffed and acted
like he was eager to
fight the next one!
That other android could
have defeated Vegeta
if he would have called
the bluff and attacked,
but Vegeta was too convincing.
Mentally, he's
impossible to beat.
He thinks of every
conceivable advantage.
And physically, he's
reached a new plateau!
I've never seen a power
quite like his before!
It's radical! Just amazing!
[GOHAN] Wow!
Do you think Vegeta's even
stronger than my Dad now?
There's a good chance,
yes. I think so.
--[KRILLIN] What?!
--[TIEN] Wow! Man o' man!
[KRILLIN] Whoa!
I say we go find them!
Vegeta may be stronger than us,
but that doesn't
make him my boss!
Yeah! Mine either!
We have just as much at stake!
We can't just
take off right now!
There's no way!
Agreed. He might need our help.
But no jumping in unless I say!
I need to get you guys
back to Goku in one piece!
Vegeta's probably
looking for him
in the mountains
as we speak.
But he's going
to be hard to find
since we can't sense
his energy level.
So spread out, lay low,
and find that tin-can!
[TIEN] Got it!
[PICCOLO] If you spot him,
call it out!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN] Right!
[thinking] Where are you?!
Coward!
Come out!
Show yourself!
How long do you want
to play hide and seek?!
If you androids experience fear,
you must feel shame, too!
So stop running
away and fight!
[VEGETA] This is ridiculous!
An android that's scared to die!
What a low-rate pile of junk!
No guts at all!
Just circuits and wires!
Fool! I'm not going to stand
here all day and night!
If you won't come out now,
I'll blast you out!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] This is
your last chance!
Come out now or else!
[VEGETA] So be it!
Huh?!
Have it your way,
you old rust-bucket!
[VEGETA growls]
No, don't! We're down here, too!
Oh, no! Oh nooo!
[VEGETA yells]
[KRILLIN screams]
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[ANDROID 20 laughs]
[ANDROID 20 yells]
--[ANDROID 20 laughs]
--[VEGETA gasps]
[ANDROID 20 yells]
[ANDROID 20 laughs]
[laughing continues]
Thanks for the
charge, you fool!
[ANDROID 20 laughs]
Darn it! He tricked me!
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] I just had to go and
give him all of that energy!
Darn! How could I?!
A mistake like that
is inexcusable!
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
His frustration is apparent.
He is no longer the cool,
confident fighter
that he was before.
Heh!
Perhaps the great Vegeta
can be beaten afterall.
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[thinking] The risk
of fighting him
in my present condition
is still too great...
I must recharge to maximum
power if I am to beat him.
I will wait for
another opportunity
to steal more energy,
but Vegeta till not make
the same mistake twice.
There must be a way
to acquire more energy...
But how?
Hmm...?
[ANDROID 20 thinking]
Who is that?
Ah, yes, it is the boy.
So he followed us afterall.
Hmm...
[ANDROID 20 thinking]
Another one I see! Hmm...
Piccolo as well!
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[ANDROID 20 thinking]
Ahh... So they are all here.
Heh, heh, heh. It seems I have
just solved my energy problem.
Yes, I will steal the energy
from these pathetic fools
one by one!
Then Vegeta is mine!
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Android 20
has formulated a plan!
Beware, defenders of Earth!
There's a thief in your midst!
And what this thief steals,
you can never get back!
On the next
Dragon Ball Z!