[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z!
As Goku recovered
from his illness,
a dark shadow loomed
over the fallen hero.
The Androids have not
forgotten their quest
to destroy Earth's
mighty champion,
and each moment finds them
closer to their goal!
Meanwhile, in the West City
suburb of Gingertown,
once busy streets
stood desolate,
as Piccolo was
forced to deal with
a far more immediate dilemma!
A terrible evil is preying upon
the city's
unsuspecting citizens!
You gotta help me!
I beg of you! Please!
Please, you have to help me!
[groans]
[NARRATOR] Horrific as it seems,
this monstrous life form
claims its victims by
absorbing their life energy
through its deadly spiked tail!
[NARRATOR] Unwilling to
allow this creature's spree
of terror to continue,
Piccolo attacked full force,
assaulting the sinister
behemoth with a dizzying flurry
of kicks and punches!
In fact, it seemed Piccolo's
new-found Super Namek powers
would easily overwhelm
the evil monster!
[NARRATOR] But the treacherous
beast proved to be
far more resilient
than it first appeared.
As it stood in defiance
of the mighty Piccolo,
the mysterious invader
prepared to unleash
a special attack of its own!
And it looked like--
the Kamehame-Ha Wave?
Can it really be?
Find out today!
[stammers]
No...
[CREATURE grunts lowly]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[CREATURE growls]
[chcukles]
Ka...
Me...
[thinking] No... it can't be!
It's impossible!
[CREATURE] Ha...
Me...
[thinking]
Where did he learn this move?
Who taught him?!
[CREATURE] Haaaaa!
[PICCOLO groans]
[grunting]
[yelling]
Aah!
I've got you now!
[yells]
[screams]
[groaning]
[CREATURE] Resistance is
useless, my friend.
In no time at all,
your energy will be mine!
[yells]
Hey, Trunks.
Any ideas on what this thing
that Piccolo's
fighting against might be?
Sorry. All we found
was its shell.
We couldn't tell what it was
or where it came from.
Do you think it's
possible that this one creature
is causing us to
sense the power levels
of Goku, Piccolo,
Vegeta, and Frieza?
Yeah. I think so.
Aaah...
I was afraid you were
gonna say that!
[KRILLIN] I hate to admit it,
but it looks like we've got
one heck of a fight
on our hands!
[birds cawing]
Your father seems to be
getting stronger every day.
Uh, he's okay. Right, Mom?
[CHICHI] Almost, Gohan.
--[CHICHI] Goku?
--[GOKU yawns]
--[GOHAN] Daddy?
[breathes heavily]
[GOHAN] Ahhh...?
[CHICHI]
We should let him rest.
But do you think
he'll wake up soon, Mom?
Possibly...
Great! I'm gonna go tell
the others the good news!
Hey everyone,
my dad's waking up!
[GOHAN laughs]
[YAMCHA gasps]
[ROSHI groans]
[MALE TV ANCHOR] Once again:
Local units of the armed forces
have been mobilized
in response to
the mass destruction
which occurred in
the West City Suburb of
Gingertown earlier today.
Whoa... Crazy!
A spokesperson
for the Army tells us
that the situation
is under control,
and that the crisis will be
resolved very shortly.
[OOLONG, ROSHI] Huh?
What... is goin' on?
This just in. We are now able
to take you "live" to Gingertown
where our correspondent
has arrived on the scene.
Now to Gingertown...
Ah... It seems we're having
some technical difficulties.
Uh--what? Now...?
To Gingertown.
I'm standing on the
outskirts of Gingertown.
Behind me you can see the dust
rising as a column of tanks
[FEMALE REPORTER] makes its way
into the heart of the city.
[FEMALE REPORTER]
The army has made no comments
regarding its tactics,
but we'll have all the details
as they become available.
[PICCOLO grunts]
[yells]
[CREATURE chuckles]
[PICCOLO groans, yells]
Ah-ha!
[beeping]
There! That's him!
You! Up there!
[ARMY COMMANDER]
We have you surrounded!
Make no attempt to resist!
Surrender immediately!
I repeat,
surrender immediately
or we will be
required to use force!
[PICCOLO groans]
What?! Can't the fools
see I'm busy?
[growls, grunts]
[CREATURE chuckles]
[ARMY COMMANDER] Open fire!
Ha-ha! Bingo!
[SOLDIER B] Commander! Look!
Ah--huh?
[CREATURE chuckles]
[grunts]
[ARMY COMMANDER] Hit him with
everything you've got, men!
Haaa...!
[ARMY COMMANDER] Aaah!
[yells]
[SOLDIERS yell]
[CREATURE] That takes care
of that little nuisance.
Now where were we?
Oh yes...
How could I have forgotten?
[PICCOLO groans, yells]
[screams]
[KAMI and PICCOLO scream]
[gasps]
Oh Kami...
[grunting]
[PICCOLO panting]
Aaah...
[birds chirping]
[ANDROID 16] Hm.
[beeping]
What was that? Something wrong?
Something is happening
to his power level.
He seems to be losing energy.
You're talking about
that fighter you said
was as strong as 17?
I am.
It's like I said,
what you're detecting
is impossible.
You're sensors are going to
have to be recalibrated,
and that's all there is to it.
[ANDROID 17]
No one is as strong as I am.
[groaning]
[chuckles]
You may have
escaped for the moment,
but I'm afraid that
with only one arm
you won't be able to
hold me off much longer.
[CREATURE]
Face it, Piccolo. Time's up.
Yes, you're right.
Hm?
It's clear that I'm
no match for you.
I can't fight without my arm...
I have no choice
but to surrender.
[laughs]
[CREATURE] So, you have
finally realized the futility
of your efforts.
But don't feel bad, Piccolo.
You will soon be
a part of something far,
far greater than you can
possibly realize!
What do you mean?
You will be absorbed into...
perfection.
[PICCOLO] All right...
But before I submit to you,
I ask that you
honor my final request.
Tell me. Who are you?
Why can I sense
Goku's energy in you?
And Frieza's? And Vegeta's?
Hmmm...
[groans]
Ha-ha-ha! Very well...
[CREATURE] Since you're
literally dying to know,
I suppose there's
no harm in telling you.
My name is Cell.
I am an Android.
You--You're an Android?
I am the single
greatest achievement
of my creator, Dr. Gero.
[grunts]
As I should have known.
You see,
in his efforts to create
a supreme fighting organism,
Dr. Gero devised a means
by which he could
fuse the cells
[CELL] of the world's
greatest fighters into one,
and then cultivate that cell
into a singular
invincible entity!
Unfortunately for
the good doctor, however,
he soon realized that his
project was far too complex
to be completed
during his lifetime.
As such,
he diverted his attention
to more immediate pursuits--
but only after he had programmed
his computer to finish
the enormous task
which he had begun.
[CELL] The computer worked
tirelessly to complete
the fusion of cells
that had been gathered
from the mightiest warriors
ever to walk the earth!
Warriors such as
the Saiyan Nappa...
The young but powerful Gohan...
And of course cells were
gathered from you, Piccolo,
so that your great
strength and determination
might also be harnessed
for our purposes.
[CELL] Most notably,
perhaps, the cells of Goku
were incorporated
into the design.
As were those of the
mighty Saiyan prince Vegeta.
Ultimately, the cells from
these sources and others
were formed into one.
And although the traits of some
were chosen by the computer
to be more dominant than
others in the final design,
at least some element
of each was retained.
[CELL chuckles]
Hm. Now I understand!
[PICCOLO] You learned
the Kamehame-Ha Wave
when you inherited Goku's cells.
That's right.
Aah! When I get my hands on--
[FRIEZA yells]
[CELL] Goku's were not the last
cells I would inherit, however.
In a most fortunate
turn of events,
Frieza paid a
brief visit to Earth.
And although it seemed that he
was mostly machine at the time,
it was possible to extract
a few of his remaining cells
before he finally met his
end at the hands of Trunks.
Dirty little Saiyan!
[KING COLD yells]
[CELL] Trunks' cells would
have also been collected,
but Dr. Gero's computer
had determined that there was
already a sufficient
collection of Saiyan powers
within my make-up.
[PICCOLO] So tell me this,
how did Dr. Gero get the cells?
I don't recall seeing
anyone suspicious around.
There is a simple explanation.
By now you must have learned
of Dr. Gero's tracking device.
Huh?
The device is very small.
Insect like.
Comparable to
a common housefly.
There, do you see it?
It's watching us now
at this very moment,
waiting for an opportunity
to gather more cells.
[gasps]
[CELL] Quite remarkable,
don't you agree?
[laughs]
[beeps]
[yells]
[laughs]
Excellent work, Piccolo.
But once again I'm afraid
you've only managed
to waste your effort.
The computer already
has the cells it needs
for my completion
back at the lab.
You're wrong!
We destroyed Dr. Gero's lab
and all of his equipment!
Luckily the computer was hidden
in a bunker
below the laboratory.
[grunting]
I see...
[PICCOLO]
It's not too late, you know.
One of the others is
bound to find that computer
[PICCOLO] and destroy it!
[CELL] Don't be absurd!
The computer
will work undisturbed
for the next 24 years--
at which time,
I'll be completed.
Now then...
let's put an end
to all of this chit-chat.
Just one more question!
[PICCOLO] Why are you here?
Why did you come to this time?
[CELL] My, you are
full of questions.
Well I suppose
I'll answer this last one.
It's quite simple, really...
You see, I cannot
realize my full power
from the energy
of humans alone.
According to the computer,
I am looking for
a very specific
source of energy.
[grunts]
More to the point,
I require the energy
of Androids 17 and 18.
What?!
[CELL] You see, the powers
of Vegeta, Goku, Frieza,
and so many others
have already been
incorporated into my being.
But even these powers
pale in comparison
to the strength
of the Androids.
It is this strength which I
must possess for myself.
Unfortunately, in the time
from which I came,
Androids 17 and 18
no longer existed.
They had somehow
been destroyed by Trunks,
[CELL] and along
with them my hopes for
ever reaching
my final, perfect stage.
Luckily, however,
I discovered that
Trunks possessed a time capsule,
which I decided
to borrow for myself.
Huh?
Aah...
[CELL laughs]
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[CELL] I dispensed of
young Trunks easily enough,
but using the time machine
itself proved to be
a much more
interesting challenge.
As I mentioned before,
in order to fit
inside the time capsule
I was forced to
regress to my larval state.
[CELL] That being accomplished,
I activated the machine
and was instantly transported
to another time and place.
A time in which
I hoped I would find
Androids 17 and 18
alive and well.
In which I would
be able to realize
the true potential of my power!
Understandably,
I could not begin my search
while still in larval form.
I had to wait until I'd
regained my fighting shape.
And so I burrowed
into the ground,
where for the last four years
I have been lying in wait--
gestating,
gathering my strength,
growing into the superior
being you see before you today!
[PICCOLO] But why did you
choose this particular time?
[CELL] I didn't.
The coordinates
were preset by Trunks.
I merely pushed a button,
and the machine
went where it was
programmed to go.
[thinking] Now it's
starting to become clear!
Trunks had set the
co-ordinates to the present
in order to tell us
that he had destroyed
the Androids in the future!
But instead,
this creep hijacked it!
The computer told me
one more thing.
[growls]
Once I have absorbed
the other Androids
I will be the most powerful
being who has ever lived!
But what for?!
You were already the strongest
creature alive in your time!
[CELL] This is true. But my
design was meant to include
the powers of
Androids 17 and 18.
Without them
I can never be complete.
I had to seek them out.
It's what I was created to do!
Of course,
it may also be the blood
of Vegeta and Frieza
coursing through my veins
[CELL] which fuels my desire
for more power.
I see...
Now, are we done talking?
Yes, I'm ready.
You've said more than enough!
[grunts]
Huh?!
[yells]
Hm?!
I just needed a little time.
You tricked me!
[CELL] I should have known
you were up to something!
I will never allow you
to become competed.
You're going down, Cell!
I intend to put an end
to your diabolical schemes
once and for all!
[yells, growls]
[NARRATOR] With Piccolo's
power fully restored,
the Super Namek is prepared
to continue his epic battle
against the most terrible evil
ever to set foot
upon the earth!
And it seems
the valiant warrior
is about to get some help!
But even with fresh troops
to aid him in his struggle,
will Piccolo be able
to stop the treacherous Cell?
Or is the key to winning the
ultimate battle still missing?
Find out on the next
exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!