[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Having lost all
of his scouters,
as well as his
top lieutenants,
Frieza called for
reinforcements!
And within moments, the
diabolical band of mercenaries
known as the Ginyu Force was
rocketing off toward Namek!
Meanwhile, despite his
painful encounter with Vegeta,
Gohan managed to
keep the location
of the final
Dragon Ball a secret...
A fact that infuriated the
evil Saiyan to no end!
Where are you, boy?!
I want that Dragon Ball!
[NARRATOR] Fueled by
his rage, Vegeta carved
a path of destruction
across the planet's surface!
You are dead!
His only goal...
To seek out Gohan and his
friends, and destroy them.
[BULMA] Why would anyone look
for us in such a horrible place?
[NARRATOR] Faced
with this threat,
Krillin came through
with a daring plan!
To... To do what?
[NARRATOR] Now, he and Gohan
are on their way to ask Guru
to awaken Gohan's
hidden powers!
But will they
be enough?
[BULMA snoring softly]
[BULMA screams]
Krillin?! Gohan?!
Is that you?!
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA] You... I've
finally found you!
Ve... Ve... Ve...
[VEGETA] You're
going to learn...
No one makes a
fool out of Vegeta!
[BULMA whimpers]
[VEGETA growls]
Now! Where's
my Dragon Ball!
[BULMA whimpers]
I-It's over there...
Don't toy with me!
[BULMA squeals]
I... I'm not...
It's right there.
I don't have time
for these lies!
[VEGETA yells]
[thinking] This... This can't
be happening! I-I told him!
Die!
Listen to me!
It's right behind you!
No! I'm too
pretty to die!
Wha--? A dream?
[VEGETA thinking]
Dammit... If Kakarot's son
truly has some sort of
Dragon Ball tracking device,
I can't afford to leave these
unguarded even for a second!
Not until I
know exactly
where he and his little
bald friend are hiding.
I have to focus...
Wait for them to make
their next move...
Sense them out...
[far-off rumbling]
[VEGETA] Hm?!
[thinking] It seems Frieza's
growing a bit restless.
I guess he's
not too happy
that I destroyed his
ship's main power core.
[thinking]
He's firing wildly.
He's blind without
his scouters.
Surely, he must have sent
for replacements by now.
But that will take time.
A few days at least.
I have to settle
this quickly.
If I can find the
last Dragon Ball,
I know I can
defeat Frieza.
But if he
gets those scouters
before I've made my
wish, it's over.
[HENCHMEN whimpering]
[thinking]
Curse you, Vegeta...
Man, it feels like the
entire planet's falling apart.
Ohh... just...
get... back here!
Don't make me come out
there after you...
Jeez! At this rate,
it's gonna take us forever
to get to
Guru's house!
But we can't risk putting
out any more power
to turn up
the speed,
or else Vegeta will
track us down for sure!
I don't know how, but
it's like he just keeps
gettin' stronger
by the minute!
As though he wasn't already
strong enough as it is.
So then... how can you
be sure that going
to see Guru
will even help?
I mean, you keep talking
about "hidden powers"...
Do you really
think I have any?
Hey, I didn't think
I had any either,
but Guru found 'em.
And you're a Saiyan!
And you're
Goku's son!
If anyone's got 'em,
I know you do.
Just trust me, okay?
Wait! No!
[BULMA grunting]
[BULMA giggles]
Come... on...!
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA whimpers]
Wait, I don't
need to get it.
It'll be safe
down there.
And when Krillin
and Gohan come back,
they can jump in
and pull it out!
Come to
think of it,
this is probably the best
thing that could've happened!
Oh well, then...
[radar beeping]
[BULMA] Huh?
[beeping continues]
Ah!
Huh...?
V-Ve... geta..?
[BULMA thinking] This is the
worst thing that could happen!
If Vegeta has
that ball,
he's going to wish
for eternal life!
And then we're all
as good as dead!
There's no way we'll
be able to stop him!
Even if Gohan does get
all those new powers
like Krillin
says he will.
Not only that...
we won't be able to wish
Yamcha back to life.
And I'll be stuck on this
stupid planet forever!
Well then...
I guess there's only
one thing to do...
If I'm going to
die in this place,
I might as well
go down fighting!
I'll show
that creep!
He just messed with
the wrong woman!
Let's see...
This one fires
the torpedoes...
This is the
laser gun...
'Kay...
[BULMA screams]
There you are!
Looks like I don't have
to fight Vegeta after all.
A little sea monster,
I can handle!
Yeah!
Piece'a cake!
[GOKU shouting]
[GOKU panting]
Kame... Hame... Haaaa!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU panting]
[panting continues]
[grunting]
[GOKU] Senzu beans...
Close one...
I guess there is
really such a thing
as training
too hard.
It won't do anyone any
good if I end up dead.
I've gotta be
more careful.
Only two more days
until I get to Namek!
Okay...
Steady as she goes...
Hm? Wha...?
[BULMA giggling]
A giant pearl!
I don't believe it...
[BULMA giggling]
[BULMA] Now, don't
you go anywhere.
I'll be back for
you in a second!
[BULMA giggling]
Ah...
All mine!
Wha...?
[BULMA screams]
Ahhh! This can't
be happening!
[BULMA] There it is!
[BULMA gasps]
What in the...
Tons of Dragon Balls!
Wait a second, those things
aren't Dragon Balls!
And they can't all
be giant pearls...
Well, whatever
they are,
I'd better just get
what I came for...
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA screaming]
[BULMA whimpering]
[BULMA] Capsule!
Escape pod capsule...
Oh no! It must have
fallen out of my pocket!
[BULMA] It's gotta
be in here somewhere!
Come on, come on!
Where are you!?
Found it!
You're gonna have
to do a lot better than that
to keep me down!
Come on! Gimme the
stupid Dragon Ball!
I mean, it's not like you're
gonna do anything with it!
[BULMA screams]
Hm?
She was just
protecting her eggs!
[BULMA] Look out!
Well, what are you
waiting for? Get moving!
[BULMA] Come on!
Come on! Hurry up!
I'm not doing this for
my health you know!
[BULMA sighs]
Phew... Too much
excitement for one day.
[BULMA screams]
[whimpering]
[BLUEBERRY] Where are the
rest of the Dragon Balls?!
[BULMA wails]
[RASPBERRY] Where's Vegeta?!
[BULMA whimpers]
Okay. If you don't
want to talk to us,
you can talk to
Lord Frieza instead.
Fuh... F-Frieza?!
C'mere!
[BULMA squeals]
[NARRATOR] Now in the clutches
of Frieza's ruthless henchmen,
the situation looks
bleak for Bulma.
With Goku
still days away,
and Krillin and
Gohan still en route
to see Guru,
the Eldest Namek,
is there anyone who can save
her from the wrath of Frieza?
The tension mounts,
as the race
for the Dragon
Balls continues...
Next time on
Dragon Ball Z!