[NARRATOR]
Previously, on Dragon Ball Z,
a new friend was helping Majin
Buu discover happiness on Earth!
But tragedy struck
when a deranged gunman
shot the innocent puppy!
[NARRATOR]
His next target was Mr. Satan,
Buu's only other
friend in the world!
[NARRATOR]
Devastated by the loss,
the child-like Majin Buu
made a desperate attempt
to restore Mr. Satan to health.
[NARRATOR]
Miraculously, Buu succeeded,
but a horrible conflict
started raging within him!
GO NOW!!!!
[NARRATOR]
The good had taken root
and the evil had to be expelled!
And in a giant puff of steam,
Majin Buu rid himself
of the wicked tendencies
that had once plagued him!
[NARRATOR] It seemed as
if Buu had won the war,
but when his nefarious vapors
started assuming physical form,
it became clear that the
true battle with his dark side
had only just begun!
[NARRATOR] In a blazing flash,
the evil Majin Buu was born!
[NARRATOR]
His first business of the day
was to pay tribute
to the murderous gunman
by giving him a taste
of his own medicine!
Aaaaugh!
[NARRATOR] Then, it was time
to face his goodly counterpart!
There can be only one!
Which of them will survive
the Battle of the Buu's?
[BUU growls]
Stop it! Who are you?
Tell me who you are first!
Me Buu! Majin Buu!
You fool! I'm Majin Buu!
Whoa! Did you hear that?
We were right!
They're both Majin Buu!
Come on, Majin Buu!
Let him have it!
Give it to him real good!
That's it! Nail him, Buu!
All right! Yeah! Go, Buu!
Oh, yeah! They're both Buu!
Uh, that makes it
hard to root for him!
[DENDE] They both seem to be
Majin Buu! Is that possible?
It is. Don't forget, Kami and
I were separate, but also one.
I just know that the struggle
was already taking place!
Only now it's on the outside!
[BUU] Hoo, hoo, hoo!
Hoo, hoo, hoo! Hoooo, hoo!
Way to get him
pinned, Majin Buu!
You're the one, big guy!
Huh?
[PICCOLO]
I don't know!
I don't like this, Dende!
He's even stronger than
the original Majin Buu!
This is not good!
[BULMA]
Trunks, you're all sweaty!
[CHICHI] Goten, you're
burning up! Here! Have a drink!
[PICCOLO] Trunks! Goten!
Playtime is over!
It's time to get back to work!
--Hmm? Huh?
--Huh?
Uh! Excuse me!
But we just got back!
Can we please take
a rest now, Piccolo?
You're too uptight!
Just leave it to us!
We're strong enough
to beat that guy already!
Why you little--
I've fought with both
of your fathers in combat!
Since before you were born!
You two don't have a clue!
Even the smallest bit of power
could mean the difference
between winning and losing!
--[CHICHI clears throat]
--Huh?
How dare you! I think
you're forgetting something!
Goten and Trunks are
boys not men. Understand?
But they need to train
No! They need to rest!
That's right!
Goku let Gohan take naps!
It's only proper!
They're children!
Yeah! What good is
all the training gonna do
if they're worn out
when the fight comes?
They're both totally exhausted!
All right! Fine!
Perhaps it would benefit!
Trunks, Goten! We'll resume our
training after you take a nap!
Right!
I get the big fluffy pillow!
[GOTEN]
Nuh-uh!
Hey! Not so fast, Goten!
You need to take a bath first.
You're all sweaty from the last
fight you were in, aren't you?!
[GOTEN]
Okay, Mom!
Hey! You too, Trunks!
Get yourself clean!
[BULMA]
I will, Mom!
Most unusual!
Never train children when
their mothers are around!
It's always trouble!
Buu make you chocolate!
[PICCOLO]
He hit him with his own attack!
[PICCOLO thinking]
You've got to be kidding me!
[DENDE thinking]
He's chocolate!
[laughs]
I don't believe it!
Look at him!
He's even meaner
looking than the last one!
[yawns]
Yaaaaaaaaah!
[PICCOLO]
Brace yourself!
[CHICHI] Oh, my goodness!
It must-must be an Earthquake!
No! We're up in the sky!
In school we always took
cover under our desks, right?!
Good idea!
[GOTEN] Hey, our moms
are under the table.
[TRUNKS]
Hmm? Really?
[GOTEN] Mhmm. They must
want our bubblegum.
[CHICHI, BULMA]
Huh?
Hm? Oh, no!
It's coming from Earth!
Man! That's incredible!
[GOHAN thinking]
What an awful power!
[OLD KAI giggles]
[laughs]
[GOHAN thinking] I've never
felt anything like this!
What's going on down there?
[laughs]
[MR. SATAN groans]
[MR. SATAN] He looks so evil.
[laughs]
Whoa! Astounding! His new power!
[KRILLIN] Hey, did you
feel that, you guys?
What just happened?
Majin Buu transformed!
Yes, and it's brought his power
to a level I can't even measure.
Not only that, but the
dark side won the battle!
He's become almost pure evil.
Hey! It couldn't be that bad!
We can still beat him, can't we?
Come on! Of course we can!
Goku said it himself! Remember?
Buu doesn't have a chance!
Not against the fusion!
Spectacular power! But I've
never felt anything this evil!
Yes! Indeed!
[laughs]
Please! Kai, sir!
There must be a way
that we can finish this
routine a little sooner.
At this rate, the planet
that I'm supposed to save
is going to be history!
Just do it to the maximum!
It'll all work out!
Sir! Please! Just hurry!
Ah!
Ha ha ha ha!
[sighs]
[MR. SATAN groans]
Hyaaaah!
Huh?
Oh, yeah! He's gone!
All right! I should've known!
Nobody wants to mess
with the mighty Mr. Satan!
No, sir-ee! I am the king!
Hahaha!
I don't blame him!
I'm twice the size
of that pink sissy!
And he didn't want
any of this anyway!
No way! Baby!
Hahahaha!
Gee! Hi, Buu! Nice day!
Sa... tan!
Hey, Bee did you see that?
Buu remembered us, boy!
He's still in there somewhere!
Piccolo, please!
Tell me the truth!
Do we even have a chance?
Well, it's hard to say!
I really don't know yet!
The fused Trunks and Goten
should put up a good fight!
If they can fit it into
their schedule that is!
Boy! I'm stuffed!
[yawns]
I need to take a nap
before I fall asleep!
Hey, Goten!
I'll race you to the bed!
Okay!
Wait, Trunks!
I want you to go hop in
the bath first! Remember?
Yes! You too, son!
'Kay! We will!
Hey! Let's take a bath together!
[TRUNKS]
No way! Forget it!
What?
[gasps]
[KRILLIN]
What is it, guys?
He's coming!
Majin Buu! He's here!
He's here!
Look! Don't attack unless he
attacks one of us first! Got it?
[NARRATOR] The ability
to sense energy levels
has led the new Majin Buu
straight to the nerve center
of the Earth's defenses!
[NARRATOR]
Aware of his friends' plight,
Gohan struggles
to remain patient,
while Goku looks on helplessly
at the bleak predicament
facing his family and friends!
[NARRATOR] What demented
plans does the new Majin Buu
have for the Earth's
special forces?
And, if given the
opportunity to fuse,
would Trunks and
Goten have a chance
against this new
incarnation of wickedness?
Stay tuned for more of the
phenomenon, on Dragon Ball Z!