[NARRATOR] Last time
on DragonBall Z,
It looked like Videl
was going to stomp
her opponent Spopovitch.
[ANNOUNCER] Spopovitch is down!
[NARRATOR] The battling beauty
matched punch-for-punch
with the hard-headed hulk
and her fancy footwork
stopped the big lug
dead in his tracks.
[NARRATOR] When she
sent Spopovitch flying
then landed a high
kick to his head,
everyone assumed
the match was over.
[VIDEL yells]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
He's down!
[NARRATOR] But no matter what
combination she threw at him,
Spopovitch kept
coming back for more!
[VIDEL growls,
SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[NARRATOR] Even a
head-spinning super kick
couldn't bring the brute down.
[SPOPOVITCH rasps]
Oh, she didn't...!
[SPOPOVITCH grunts,
bones creaking]
[VIDEL whimpers]
What the...?!
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[NARRATOR] Videl tried to catch
her breath high above the crowd.
But when Spopovitch
came after her,
she knew she was in trouble.
Now that the bald-headed bully
has an unlimited supply
of super strength, does this
mean it's lights out for Videl?
Find out today on Dragon Ball Z!
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
Spopovitch is flying in the air!
Now there's no place left
for Videl to hide!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
No way...
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[VIDEL whimpers]
Whoa... Hey... Don't you have
to have a license to do that?
Look! How does he do that?!
He could never fly before!
What is his secret?!
[KILLA mumbles incoherently]
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[VIDEL thinking]
So he can fly, too?!
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[VIDEL gasps]
[yelling continues]
[VIDEL screams]
--No!
--An energy wave!
[VIDEL grunting]
[VIDEL yells]
[grunts]
[CROWD murmuring]
[VIDEL whimpers]
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[VIDEL grunts]
[VIDEL thinking]
This guy is a... monster!
Ah! I don't believe it!
But it's a good thing this guy's
energy waves aren't very strong.
You're wrong.
Huh?
The guy's got some sort
of unlimited power.
He'll lose the match
if he kills her.
"Unlimited power?"
I don't know how
he's doing it
but somehow Spopovitch is using
powers he's never had before!
Huh?
It's strange...
But the last time he fought
in this tournament,
I'm positive he couldn't fly
or throw an energy attack.
But what does that mean, Dad?
I don't know...
I don't know how he could have
changed this much, Gohan.
[SPOPOVITCH growls quietly]
[VIDEL thinking]
He doesn't scare me!
I'm the daughter of Mr. Satan,
the man who defeated Cell!
I know I can beat him...
and I will!
[VIDEL yells]
[yelling continues,
SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH snarls,
VIDEL grunts]
[blows landing,
VIDEL grunting]
[VIDEL grunts]
[VIDEL whimpers]
Videl's hit the
ground hard!
Let's hope that she can get up!
[VIDEL grunting]
Aah...
Oh! Videl is struggling
to get back in the fight!
What willpower!
What determination!
No...
I will never give up! Never!
[VIDEL yells]
[blows landing,
SPOPOVITCH grunting]
[VIDEL gasps]
No way!
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[VIDEL grunts]
[VIDEL yells]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
Oh! Poor girl!
This is awful!
What a nightmare!
Videl doesn't have a chance!
I hate to say it, but I think
her luck has officially run out.
[MR. SATAN grunting]
[MR. SATAN] Hmm...
You know, I probably
shouldn't go all out
in this first match...
It'll make for a better show
if I save some of my special
techniques for the final.
[MR. SATAN grunts]
It's never been easy controlling
my incredible strength.
Hmm...
But it is my job to give the
people what they paid for.
[knocking]
Uh, Mr. Satan... I thought
you might wanna know
that Videl is about to lose her
match to Spopovitch!
Come on! Not this again.
You know what?
You got it backwards.
Videl is gonna win!
Heee!
Sir! You really
should take a look!
[MR. SATAN] Can't you see I'm
getting warmed up
for my next match?!
So for the last time, I'm
not worried about Videl!
Come and get me when she wins!
Uhh... Oh...
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[VIDEL yells]
[blows landing,
SPOPOVITCH grunting]
[VIDEL growls]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
You're going down!
[VIDEL screaming,
SPOPOVITCH laughing]
Look at that! Spopovitch
has given Videl the toss!
If she goes out of the ring,
she'll lose the match!
[VIDEL thinking] I don't know
if I have the strength
to stop myself!
[VIDEL yells]
[VIDEL gasps]
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts,
VIDEL screams]
Wow! I don't believe it,
but Spopovitch has saved Videl
from falling out of the ring!
What on earth could
he be planning to do now?!
Oh no!
Argh... That creep
is just playing with her!
[YAMU growls]
It appears that Videl
could be down for the count!
She doesn't seem to be
moving at all!
This might be it, folks!
[GOHAN thinking]
Stay down, Videl!
It's over! Don't get up!
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[VIDEL grunts]
[chuckling continues]
[VIDEL whimpers]
Videl! Don't stand up!
[CROWD cheers]
Yeah-ha!
Whoa! Look out! Now that's
what I call one tough fighter!
Alright! Videl is
back on her feet!
She stood up...
[VIDEL growls]
[yelling]
No, Videl! Don't do it!
You can't beat him!
You've got to give up now!
[growling continues]
[KRILLIN growls]
[VIDEl yells]
[SPOPOVITCH grunts,
VIDEL screams]
No! That's enough!
[VIDEL screams]
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
{VIDEL grunts]
[VIDEL yells]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[VIDEL grunting]
Oh! Poor Videl!
I don't know how much
more of this she can take!
I've got to stop him!
[VIDEL grunting]
[ANNOUNCER]
This is just terrible!
Spopovitch is using Videl
as a punching bag!
I don't know why he
doesn't end this now!
He's completely out of control!
[VIDEL grunting]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[POLICE MAN A] Hey, Chief,
you sure we ain't gonna
miss Videl's match?!
[CHIEF] Ah, don't worry
about it, boys!
I know she's gonna make
it to the final round
and then we'll be seeing a whole
lot of her, you can count on it!
Hey, you guys, guess what?!
Videl's getting beat up
and it looks bad!
[ALL] Not Videl?!
Yeah, Videl! And we better
show her some support
or else she's gonna
lose the match! Come on!
[POLICMEN yell]
[VIDEL grunting]
[SPOPOVITCH growls]
[VIDEL whimpers]
[growling continues]
[SPOPOVITCH snarls]
[VIDEL grunting]
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
Oh, somebody please
stop that guy!
[BLONDE WOMAN]
I can't bare to watch anymore!
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[VIDEL grunts]
[SPOPOVITCH roars]
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[CROWD gasping]
[ANNOUNCER yelps]
[VIDEL grunts]
[whimpering]
That's enough! Give up,
Videl! Please give up!
There's no way you can beat him!
[CROWD gasping,
VIDEL grunting]
Look, Videl...
I don't want to interfere
but now might be a
good time to call it a day!
Come on, whatta ya say? Are you
ready to throw in the towel now?
[VIDEL grunts]
No! No way!
I can... still beat this guy!
Videl! Come on,
stop being so stubborn!
You're just gonna get
hurt out there!
It's been a trick all along!
Spopovitch knows
he can beat you!
He's playing with you now!
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[VIDEL growls]
[VIDEL gasps]
[VIDEL shrieks]
[SPOPOVITCH yells]
[GOHAN screams]
[VIDEL screams]
Ah! That's it!
He's gone too far!
[KRILLIN growls]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Nooo! Stop! Please!
--That monster!
--[ERASA sobs]
--[POLICMEN growl]
--Whatta ya say?!
Do you think we should
arrest that guy, Chief?!
[GOHAN growls]
Hey! No. Stop! Just calm down!
Don't do it, Gohan!
You're not going out there!
[SPOPOVITCh growls]
[CROWD gasping]
[SPOPOVITCH laughs]
[VIDEL screams]
[SPOPOVITCH growls,
screaming continues]
[VIDEL screaming]
[ANNOUNCER] Spopovitch has
gone too far this time!
This could be a
violation of the rules!
Ow! It hurts just to watch!
[CHICHI screams]
Please! Somebody has
got to do something!
Videl will make the
perfect wife for Gohan
but they'll never get together
if she gets squashed like a bug!
Gohan...!
[GOHAN growls]
[VIDEL screams]
[VIDEL sobs, shrieks]
[GOHAN yells]
[snarling]
That does it!
This has gone on way too long!
I'm taking him down!
[GOHAN growls]
No, don't!
Don't go out there!
Calm down, Gohan!
[GOHAN] Don't try to stop me!
[SPOPOVITCH growls,
VIDEL shrieks]
[GOHAN] Videl!
[YAMU] That's enough!
Stop playing games, Spopovitch!
[SPOPOVITCH] Hrn?!
[GOHAN gasps]
[gasping]
Don't you remember that we have
far more important things to do?
[SPOPOVITCH whimpers]
Finish it, right now!
[SPOPOVITCH groans,
VIDEL whimpers]
[VIDEL grunts]
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
Oh my... Videl? It's over!
She's out of the ring!
[GOHAN] Videl?! Are you okay?!
[VIDEL whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER grunts]
Should I call out a
stretcher for her?
No! I'll take her myself.
--[VIDEL whimpers]
--[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[chuckling continues]
[GOHAN] Spopovitch!
[GOHAN growls]
[SPOPOVITCH] Hrrgh?!
Listen... Next time...
It's you and me!
And I'll win!
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
Krillin, hey! Do you
have any Senzu beans?
[KRILLIN] Uh, no, Goku.
I didn't think I'd need them!
Okay... Then...
I'll be right back. I'm going
to see Korin to get some!
Hey, don't worry, Gohan.
Goku went to get some
Senzu beans to fix her up!
Oh, he did? Alright!
That's my dad!
[MR. SATAN] What? What?!
Whatta ya mean Videl
lost the match?!
You--! You're lying!
That can't be!
We both know that
next to me,
Videl is the strongest in
the world! Poor girl!
The pressure must have
gotten to her!
Daddy's coming, Sugarbeet!
[FRIAR groans]
[FRIAR] Oh, why
do I even bother?
[DOCTOR] Oh my,
most unfortunate...
[MR. SATAN] Videl! Videl?!
[running footsteps]
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[VIDEL whimpers]
No! Oh, my little girl!
She's okay, sir.
But she's gonna need
some time to heal.
Oh yeah?! Who are you?
Are you the one who put my
daughter in the hospital?!
[MR. SATAN growls]
[DOCTOR] No, Mr. Satan.
You should be thanking this
young man for bringing Videl in.
Yeah! That's right...
..It wasn't him!
It was Spopovitch, wasn't it?!
He's the one that did this!
Thanks a lot, kid!
I'll get you an autograph.
What...? That's great...
I guess...?
Sure... We don't need you
now, boy. You can go!
[GOHAN] Uh... right.
[VIDEL groans]
Gohan...! Wait, come back!
[VIDEL yells]
[GOHAN] Hm?
[VIDEL whimpers]
That guy... Spopovitch...
Go get him!
Yeah...
I just have to win
my next match,
and I promise I'll take care
of him for you!
What are you
talking about, Videl?
There's no way that kid
can beat Spopovitch!
But don't worry, Sweetheart.
Your daddy will get him for you!
[MR. SATAN screams]
Oh no! Videl!
Don't tell me that that kid
is your boyfriend?!
I won't allow it!
Do you hear me?!
I do not approve of this!
You know I've always said that
if you have a boyfriend,
then he must
be strong like me!
Not a feeble, little twerp!
How can he protect
my little girl?!
[DOCTOR] Mr. Satan!
Quiet please!
[MR. SATAN] Uh! Oh,
uh? Oh, of course...
[KORIN] Here are the
Senzu beans, Goku.
[GOKU] Thanks a lot, Korin!
Remember, my friend. I wouldn't
use all those beans at once.
Alright?
I have a feeling you're going
to need every one of them.
Yeah.
Me, too!
[NARRATOR] Goku has the
Senzu beans to heal Videl,
but he'd better hold onto a
handful in case of emergency.
As the World Martial Arts
Competition continues,
there is sure to be more
casualties along the way.
Korin senses trouble
on the horizon.
And after watching Spopovitch
turn into a super-powered psycho
Goku has every reason
to believe him.
What awaits the next competitor
who steps into the ring?
Find out on the next
Dragon Ball Z!