[NARRATOR]
Last time on DragonBall Z...
The deranged Dr. Gero,
driven by his desire
to destroy Goku, created
three killer androids
to carry out his vengeful plan.
Activated first was Android 17.
A real microchip off the
old block, whose own
passion for power lead to the
demented doctor's demise.
Android 17 was joined
by his synthetic sister,
Android 18, batteries and
bad attitude included.
The two conspired and pulled the
plug on the diabolical doctor
and took control of
his evil operation.
Then they awoke the
mechanized monster,
Android 16, a bionic
behemoth whose few
words spoken revealed
that he was programmed
to pursue Goku
and pulverize him.
Bedridden battling
a mysterious virus,
Goku makes an easy target
for these hi-tech horrors.
Vegita, ignoring Trunks', the
boy from the future's warning,
decided to face
the androids alone.
[ANDROID 17]
Good.
[NARRATOR] What ensued was
an earth shaking showdown
between Android and Saiyan!
Vegita's over inflated ego
and newly acquired Super Saiyan
powers served him well,
but it was obvious that Android
18 was the superior fighter.
[NARRATOR] It looked as
though Vegita would be down
for the count but that's
when the good guys arrived
to offer their support. But once
again Vegita's foolish pride
got the best of him and
he refused their help.
[TRUNKS]
Hey, are you okay?
Of course I am!
I told you I don't
need your help,
and I don't want it either!
[NARRATOR]
It was then that Android 17
made a deal with Vegeta.
[ANDROID 17] I'm willing to
stand aside and let you fight,
as long as you fight alone.
But if any one of these
"friends" of yours tries
to assist you in any way...
I'll be forced to step in.
Bring it on!
As you wish.
[grunting]
[NARRATOR] Vegeta and Android 18
traded blow for blow,
but as the Saiyan
avoided a move by 18,
she struck him with
a bone-crushing kick.
[VEGETA groans]
No!
[VEGITA groaning]
Father!
[TRUNKS]
[TRUNKS growling]
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[TRUNKS groans]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Let's get them!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
Uh, wait guys!
Don't you think you're being
just a little too hasty?
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO groans]
[VEGITA grunting]
[TIEN grunts]
[ANDROID 17]
This is too easy!
[TIEN grunting, yelling]
Android!
[TIEN gasping]
[ANDROID 18] You should
have kept your little friends
out of this, Vegeta.
[TRUNKS growls]
[ANDROID 18]
Hm?
No don't!
[TRUNKS, VEGETA groan]
[VEGITA, TRUNKS groan]
[TRUNKS groans]
Hmph.
[KRILLIN whimpering]
This isn't good!
[KRILLIN]
What's he doing over there?
Why isn't he fighting
with the others?
He's just standing there
like some kind of statue.
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
What is he up to?
[PICCOLO grunts, growls]
[TIEN grunting]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[PICCOLO groaning]
[ANDROID 17]
Even their strongest warriors
fall by the wayside.
Oh no! Piccolo!
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
[ANDROID 17 cackles]
[VEGITA growling]
[VEGITA groans]
[grunting]
[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGITA grunting]
[ANDROID 18]
He doesn't know when to quit!
[VEGITA groaning]
What's it going to take
to get through to you,
Vegeta? You've been beaten.
[VEGITA groaning]
[VEGETA yelling]
[VEGITA panting]
Hmph.
[VEGITA groaning]
[ANDROID 17]
How curious...
Vegeta's hair has
changed color again.
Yes. And that strange
glow has faded, too.
It's the same with
this young boy.
I don't have any files on him.
[ANDROID 17]
Neither do I.
[ANDROID 18]
I wonder who he is?
It doesn't really
matter, does it?
Whoever he is...
...he's no threat to us.
[KRILLIN whimpering]
Oh no! Great!
I'm on my own now.
[KRILLIN] Maybe if I just stay
quiet, they won't notice me.
[KRILLIN screams]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[MASTER ROSHI snoring]
[MARON laughing]
Nice going, Maron!
You're doing great!
[MARON laughing]
[SHADES]
What's going on, babe?
Hi!
Hey, uh, how'd you like
to go for a little ride?
[BUDDY] Swim on over
and we'll give you a lift.
Oh! Sounds great!
[MARON screaming]
Oh! Save me! Help me! Save me!
[MASTER ROSHI snoring]
[MARON screaming]
Please girls...
Not now...
I'm too tired!
[MARON screaming]
[TURTLE]
It's okay, Maron.
You're safe. You're on land now.
Wow! You saved my life,
Turtle! Thank you!
[SHADES]
Hey babe! Let's go cruisin'!
Um. Well...
I'll be right there!
Hey, Turtle! Let go!
Don't go Maron.
You said you were going to wait
for Krillin to come back.
Oh. That's right.
Okay. I guess I
should keep my word
and wait for Krillin.
Thanks, Turtle!
Hey, come on.
Yeah, babe. What's the hold up?
[TURTLE growls]
Hey there! What's your
friend's name huh?
Uh Turtle.
Well, that's real nice...
but no pets, in the boat, dude.
[SHADES]
Hey what's with him?
[BUDDY] I think he's trying
to tell us something.
[SHADES] Are you sure? He's got
a strange look in his eyes.
I think he's frozen
or something?
Step aside. Or we'll
turn you into soup.
Do you catch my drift?
[TURTLE grunts]
[SHADES, BUDDY laughing]
[SHADES, BUDDY grunting]
[MARON shrieks]
[SHADES, BUDDY groan]
[MARON whimpers]
Oh gosh!
[SHADES, BUDDY groaning]
[TURTLE grunting]
[MARON gasps]
[SHADES, BUDDY scream]
[BUDDY, SHADES]
He's a monster!
Let's get out of here!
Wow! You're strong, Turtle.
[MARON giggling]
[TURTLE groaning]
Turtle, you saved me!
[TURTLE gasps]
Hey. What's wrong?
Hello?
No! Please, Maron!
It's wrong! You and me!
I love ya, but I can't!
[MARON growls]
It's only a kiss Turtle!
I was trying to thank you!
[TURTLE groans]
Maron!
[MASTER ROSHI snoring]
[MASTER ROSHI]
H-hey, where did everybody go?
[KRILLIN whimpering]
You look scared. Just relax.
You are not the one
we're looking for, okay?
We want Goku.
[KRILLIN gasps]
This one seems to be
at a loss for words.
Goodbye then. Come on, let's go!
[ANDROID 17]
Let's go find Goku!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
And just why didn't you
ask him where Goku is?
[ANDROID 17]
Don't be ridiculous.
Sure, we could force him
to tell us easily enough.
But, then we wouldn't
get to have the fun
of finding Goku ourselves.
I see.
Well, bye!
[KRILLIN]
Those cold-hearted machines!
How can they be so calm?
[ANDROID 18] Really, I don't
understand why you insist
on behaving so foolishly, 17.
[ANDROID 17]
What's so foolish about
wanting to have a little fun?
[ANDROID 17]
What are you looking at, 16?
You two made too much noise.
You scared the birds away.
[ANDROID 17]
Birds?
[ANDROID 18] Listen! It
doesn't look like any cars
are going to be
coming down this road.
So if you still
want to find one,
maybe we should fly
somewhere a little busier!
[ANDROID 17]
Yes, of course.
That's a wonderful idea, 18.
[CHICHI]
My poor Goku!
I hope the medicine is working.
I know he will get well soon.
I just can't give up hope!
Ah!
[GOHAN]
Oh boy! There it is!
Home at last!
[GOHAN]
Wow! What a view!
Gohan! Listen! Can we
go by my house first?
Uh-- But I wanna go
see my Dad, Bulma.
He's not feeling well, remember?
I know, but I promise
I won't take long! Okay?
It feels like we've
been gone forever,
and I really need
some more supplies.
P.U.! Little Trunks needs
his diaper changed!
Being a mother really
isn't easy, you know.
I have to get Baby Trunks
some fresh diapers
and then I have to feed
him. It's a lot of work.
Gohan I vote that we all
go to Bulma's house.
I want some food!
[BABY TRUNKS babbling]
Well, you guys win.
It's three against one.
[BULMA]
Thanks a lot Gohan!
My Mom will be really
glad to see you!
[KRILLIN]
I-it's up to me.
If I let them get away,
they're gonna find Goku
and squash him!
[ANDROID 17]
Yes, let's go.
I'm sure there will be plenty
of cars to choose from
once we find a more
populated area.
[ANDROID 18]
And while we're at it,
I really wouldn't mind
replacing these torn-up clothes.
Well, are you ready to
begin our search, 16?
Yes.
No! Stop!
[ANDROID 17]
And what do you want now?
Stop! You guys leave Goku alone.
He's sick! He can't
fight you now!
Goku hasn't done
anything to you!
Why are you after him?
[ANDROID 17] 16 has been
programmed to destroy Goku.
So that's what
we're going to do!
Why? You don't have to do that!
[ANDROID 17]
We're only following Dr. Gero's
master plan.
Just listen to yourselves!
Did you forget?
Dr. Gero is gone!
You took care of that!
Yes, I haven't
forgotten about that.
But this, friend, is a game!
What, do you mean?
This is just a game?
Is that all?
That's right!
Yes, and finding Goku
is a part of the game!
That's why we did not
ask you where he is!
No! Stop this!
I beg of you, please don't
go after Goku! Please!
[KRILLIN]
You don't have to do this!
No. I am programmed
to destroy Goku.
[ANDROID 17]
There you go, pal!
[ANDROID 17] Now if you'll
excuse us, we have work to do.
[ANDROID 17]
Stop worrying about Goku
and take care of
your other friends.
They look like they could
use some senzu beans.
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[KRILLIN]
Good Luck!
Bye!
[NARRATOR] The androids' search
and destroy mission has begun.
It's only a matter
of time before
the synthetic psychos
find their target.
Although Krillin tried
to persuade them
to end their pursuit, they are
driven by a prime directive
to hunt down and destroy Goku,
who lies helpless and unaware
of the danger headed his way.
Now Vegita, Trunks,
Piccolo and Tien
are out of commission
and Krillin is on his own.
Can he conquer his fear and stop
the three computerized crazies
from reaching Goku?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!