[birds chirp]
[BOY] Yahoo!
[FARMER]
Good one, Billy!
[NARRATOR]
Five years have passed
since Goku and his friends
thwarted the evil
King Piccolo's plans
for global conquest.
Thanks to their
heroic efforts,
the shadow of doom was
lifted from the world,
and a new day of
hope has dawned.
For in the years since
Piccolo's defeat,
it has been a time
of rebuilding, healing,
prosperity, and peace
for the citizens of Earth.
But, unknown to them,
at this very moment,
a new threat to
humankind is hurtling
through the
solar system.
And as the mysterious invader
makes its final approach
to Earth, one
thing is certain:
The peaceful era the
human race has enjoyed
for the last
five years
is about to come
crashing to an end!
[birds chirp]
[CHICHI]
Gohan!
Gohan?
It's time to
come in! Gohan!
Ah!
This one ought to do.
Yaa!
[rumbling]
[crashing sound]
Hey, Gohan!
Goku, do you think you've
got enough fire wood there?
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] Yeah.
This should last us a
while, don't you think?
[CHICHI] Ugh. You're
going to hurt yourself
doing that one
of these days.
[GOKU] Aww, I'm fine.
Where's Gohan?
[CHICHI]
I don't know...
But I think you'd better
go find him, don't you?
You two are supposed be at
Master Roshi's pretty soon.
Oh, yeah!
That's right!
[CHICHI] You better
take the flying nimbus.
You don't want to be
late for your reunion!
[GOKU]
Okay! Bye ChiChi!
[CHICHI]
Goku! Be careful!
Ugh. I'm going to worry
myself to death...
[FARMER hums]
Phew-oo-ee! This job's
bigger than I thought!
Hm? Hm?
What is that?
[FARMER yells]
My gosh, it hit!
I guess I better
go check it out.
Goodness, why me?
[brakes screech]
[FARMER] I better bring
my pea-shooter.
[FARMER stammers]
[FARMER]
I don't like this...
That's no meteor.
It's made of steel!
Wh-What in the world?
I'll be darned.
Uh?!
So, the creatures on this
planet are still alive.
Kakarot has
failed us!
You're on my
p-property.
[cocks gun]
[RADITZ]
Is that so? Hmm...
Your power
level is puny.
Heh. Level 5.
Don't you come any closer!
Look! I'll use this thing!
Aahhh!
Huh?
[RADITZ] Hm?
Hmm...
[FARMER screams]
Heh. What a fragile
breed of people...
[beeping]
I'm picking up a high
power-level from over there.
It must be him.
Prepare yourself,
Kakarot!
[GOHAN cries]
[GOHAN] I want my Daddy.
I want to go home.
Daddy!
Uh, anyone?
[GOHAN sobs]
Uh, hey, Mr. Butterfly!
Wait! Come back!
I'm not gonna hurt you!
I just wanna look!
Aww, c'mon! You want me
to climb up there? Okay.
Aahh!
Aww... Hold on.
I'm coming!
Say, are you sure there's not
an elevator on this thing?
Uh?
[rustling in bushes]
[GOHAN]
Uh... Hello?
M-Mister Butterfly?
[SABERTOOTH roars]
[GOHAN]
Uh, n-nice kitty...
[SABERTOOTH growls]
[GOHAN]
I know... Play dead!
[GOHAN chuckles]
[SABERTOOTH growls]
Aah! My hat is gone!
[GOHAN yells]
No! My Daddy
gave me that hat!
[GOHAN sobs]
My hat!
Give me back my hat!
You can't have it!
Aaahhh--
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN]
Whoa...
[GOHAN cries]
Hey! Gohan!
[GOHAN]
Okay.
Aaahh...
Mommy! Daddy!
Oh! Well, hello there!
You're a pretty bird.
It's nice to meet you.
[BIRD chirps]
So, do you have a name?
I'm Gohan.
Aahh. Hey, wait!
Aahh! Mommy!
Daddy! Help me!
Huh?
[growling]
Hm? Hey you...
That hat!
That's Gohan's! It belongs to
my son. Have you seen him?
[growling]
Where did you
get his hat?
I said, where
did you get it?
[SABERTOOTH whimpers]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN]
Aah! Help me!
[GOKU] Gohan!
Mommy! Daddy!
Aaaahhh!
[GOKU] Gohan!
Can you hear me?
Gohan?
[gasps]
Gohan!
It's Daddy!
Hang on, son!
I'll be right there!
Just a little farther!
Huh?!
[GOHAN]
Aaahhh! Daddy!
Hang on, Gohan!
Help!
Daddy!
Hurry! It's dark--Uh?
[GOHAN screams]
Daddy! Help!
Ah!
Gohan!
[GOHAN yells]
Huh?
[GOHAN yells and sobs]
Help! I'm stuck! I can't
get down! Wahh! Wahh!
[GOHAN sobs]
Daddy! Thank you, Daddy!
Oh, I was so scared!
[GOKU] But, how did you
get all the way up here?
Wow, that's strange.
Daddy, uh...
I lost my hat.
What? Silly... No you didn't.
It's on your head!
Now let's go get
you cleaned up.
Then you can come
with me to meet
all my friends at
Master Roshi's!
That's my boy!
[CROWD murmurs]
[laughter]
[horns honk]
Bah! Miserable
little vermin.
[PICCOLO gasps]
What is that? I've never
felt such so much power.
It can't be Goku...
It's too horrible.
Who is that?
[RADITZ] Excuse me
for dropping in.
I'm trying to find
a man named Kakarot.
I thought you were him.
[PICCOLO]
Well, you thought wrong.
Now turn around and get out
of here, before I get angry!
Someone's having
a bad day.
Believe me, you have
no idea. Now get lost.
[RADITZ laughs]
Oh, you'd like that,
wouldn't you?
Power level 322.
I can tell you're
not from this planet...
But you'd be a
fool to attack me
with such an...
insufficient power.
Now listen to me!
You came here!
I have no intention
of starting a fight!
I do.
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO thinking] All right!
If that's the way
he wants it...
[PICCOLO grunts]
Aahhh!
Heh.
Huh?!
[RADITZ laughs]
[RADITZ]
Impressive!
You actually managed to
singe some of my leg hair.
But allow me to demonstrate
a more effective attack.
It's one of my favorites.
I call it a Double Sunday.
Now... See if you
can follow this one!
[beeping]
Well, I guess it's your
lucky day, green man.
[beeping]
There it is. just on the edge
of my scouter's range.
And it's big...
It must be the largest
power level on this planet!
It's Kakarot...
This time I'm sure!
[panting]
I don't believe it...
I hit him full force,
and he didn't even flinch!
This guy could
be a problem.
Have you forgotten
your pride, Kakarot?
We are Saiyans... The mightiest
warriors in the universe!
I can still remember
the day that we first
sent you to this
planet as an infant...
We had high hopes for
you then, Kakarot.
Why have you not carried
out your mission?
Kakarot!
[NARRATOR] Who is this
mysterious Saiyan warrior
that now darkens the
skies with his presence?
His search for the
one named Kakarot
has already led
him to Piccolo...
One of the most powerful
fighters on Earth.
Could it lead him
to Goku as well?
The answers to these
burning questions
will soon
be revealed...
And Goku will discover
the secrets of his past!
Next time on
Dragon Ball Z!