[CELL] No, this isn't
happening, I am Cell!
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
it looked as though Vegeta
had the upperhand on Cell.
But don't count
Cell out quite yet.
Knowing of the Saiyan's
thirst for battle,
he lured Vegeta into
a mind-boggling agreement.
Now go and absorb your android.
Hopefully the next
time I see you,
you won't be in
such a pitiful state.
It's embarassing!
[NARRATOR] But will
allowing Cell to power up
be Vegeta's fatal mistake?
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL gasps]
[NARRATOR] Not if Trunks
has anything to say about it.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Krillin held the fate
of the other Androids in the
palm of his hands... literally.
With one flick of the switch,
Krillin could shut down
Android 18 for good,
preventing Cell from
reaching his completion.
[BOTH gasp]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[NARRATOR] But at the
crucial moment of decision,
Krillin opted to spare the
beautiful android's life.
You shouldn't be here.
Look, if cell finds you,
then we're all doomed!
Please go.
[NARRATOR] Has Krillin's
fit of compassion
sealed the planet's fate?
And if things
weren't bad enough,
Cell has stumbled
upon the alcove
where the androids are hiding.
[NARRATOR] The scales of victory
are tipping in Cell's favor,
today on Dragon Ball Z!
[thinking] Yes! I have found
what I have been looking for!
Soon, 18 you will be mine!
[CELL] Once I have consumed her,
I will be of perfect
mind and body!
The ultimate warrior!
An Android with no equal
in power, speed or technique!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[thinking] On no! The androids!
And Krillin's with them!
They haven't noticed
we're up here!
You could've shut me down
but you didn't.
What were you trying to achieve?
Well... Y-You see...
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[thinking] Would you
stop looking at me
with those puppy dog eyes?!
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
I don't have much
time to explain, okay?!
But Cell is hot on your tail and
he'll do anything to absorb you!
And if that happens,
the entire planet is doomed!
Which means, you have to
get yourself out of here now!
[TRUNKS] Hey!
Cell knows where you are!
--[CELL] Hm?!
--[VEGETA] Huh?!
--[ANDROID 18 gasps]
--[ANDROID 16 growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[KRILLIN] Ah, man, it's him!
[CELL chuckles]
I won't let you do it!
[TRUNKS growls]
I see... Trunks wants to
test out his powers as well.
[TRUNKS growls]
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[CELL snarls]
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS shouting]
[CELL grunting]
[CELL growls]
[TRUNKS growls]
Raaaugh!
[CELL grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[CELL growls]
[CELL grunts]
[VEGETA growls]
Ah, man! I'd sure like to
know what kind of vitamins
Trunks is taking!
He's masked his energy...
[TRUNKS] Krillin! Get
the Android away fast!
Cell is probably
moving underground!
[KRILLIN] C'mon!
We don't have much time
before Mr. Grumpy
digs himself out!
[ANDROID 18] Right!
Let's go, 16!
Are you still there?!
Do not... worry about me...
Huh...?
My circuitry is much too
damaged... Save yourself!
[ANDROID 18] 16, I...
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[BOTH yell]
[CELL laughs]
[BOTH growl]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Stupid boy, this is too good an
opportunity for you to screw up!
[CELL chuckles]
Huh?!
[VEGETA snarls]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS yells]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Aaahhh...
So nice to see you, 18!
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[CELL] Hmm...?
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[CELL chuckles]
From the looks of it, 16,
I'd say your batteries
are running low.
Now, thanks to Vegeta,
I will finally reach the
perfection that
my designer intended.
Vegeta! I should have known!
Yes... He is a brave one.
Incredibly stupid,
but brave nonetheless.
[VEGETA] Hurry it up already!
Would you just consume the
Android and be done with it?
I haven't got all day!
Imbecile!
[VEGETA grunts]
[TRUNKS yells]
[VEGETA grunting]
Vegeta!
[BULMA] Did you
say "Vegeta"? Why?
What's going on? Tell me!
Hey! Answer me,
Piccolo! Answer me!
Answer!
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
[thinking] This planet only
has one hope left...
You better be
training hard, Goku.
[VEGETA chuckles]
I am in your debt, Vegeta.
Children can be such a bother.
[CELL laughs]
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[KRILLIN growls]
[KRILLIN yells]
[yelling continues,
blows landing]
[KRILLIN grunts]
Rat bag...
[CELL grunts]
[ANDROID 16 yells]
[blows landing,
ANDROID 16 yells]
Don't you find it remarkable
how powerless you are now?
I can't wait to see
what my completion will do.
[CELL laughs]
--[CELL grunts]
--[ANDROID 16 grunts]
[ANDROID 18 growls]
Raaaugh!
[ANDROID 18 shouts]
[ANDROID 18 groans]
[VEGETA] Hngh?!
[TRUNKS snarls]
[TRUNKS] You're wrong, Father!
You can't let him
reach his final form!
There's a good chance that he'll
become stronger than both of us!
[VEGETA chuckles]
But that's the thrill...
Don't you want to see this
power he keeps talking about?
No! I've seen it all my life!
[CELL growls]
I've lived through the horrors
a force like that creates...
And I won't let it
happen in this time too!
Even if it means
taking you... down!
You stop me?!
[VEGETA chuckles]
I know you don't
have the guts to
challenge your own, dear father.
Your feelings will stop you.
That's what makes you weak.
[TRUNKS growls]
[VEGETA gasps]
[yelling]
[VEGETA screams]
[GOHAN whimpers quietly]
[whimpering continues]
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN growls]
I'm really sorry, Dad...
I bet you wish I
wasn't even here, right?
So that I wouldn't
slow you down so much?
He-He-Hey!
You know I'd never think
something like that about
my big, super-cool son!
Ahh... Right!
Good. Alright, Gohan,
let's get you tucked in
and tomorrow we'll put
in another hard day, okay?
[GOHAN] Okay!
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[CELL chuckles]
[ANDROID 18 whimpers]
[growling]
--[ANDROID 18] Hyaah!
--[CELL] Hrrgh!
[ANDROID 18 growls]
Ahh.. Arrghhh...
Haaah!
[CELL grunts]
[CELL growls]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
--[CELL laughs]
--[ANDROID 18 growls]
[KRILLIN growls]
I've got to do something!
No... No, 18!
[CELL laughs]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[CELL chuckles]
No!
[CELL laughs]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
I can't watch!
[CELL bellows]
[TRUNKS growls]
[grunting]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
There's not much time!
You've got to hurry
and get out of here!
[CELL growls]
Why, you little...
[TRUNKS growls]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[TRUNKS yells]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
Leave me be... I am done...
I'm staying with you!
[KRILLIN] Hey, big guy.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
What? What do you want?
Well... He actually did it.
The boy is stronger
willed than I thought.
Too bad he's playing
the wrong side!
[grunting]
[CELL growls]
[growling continues]
Yes... A brilliant plan.
Ah!
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL] My destiny awaits!
Your time has expired...
Android 18!
[VEGETA growls]
Huh...?
Why you...
[CELL growls]
Solar Flare!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[VEGETA grunts]
[KRILLIN] Oh, great! Not again!
[grunting]
[CELL chuckles]
Time to devour the
last morsel and become whole!
[KRILLIN growls]
[KRILLIN yells]
[ANDROID 18 whimpers]
[CELL chuckles]
You monster!
[ANDROID 18 snarls]
[ANDROID 18 grunting,
CELL laughing]]
[CELL yells]
[ANDROID 18]
No! I can't be part of you!
[ANDROID 18 screams]
[KRILLIN] You let her go!
[grunting]
18, no!
[TRUNKS grunts]
Huh?!
[CELL grunts]
[CELL yells]
The transformation has begun.
At last I will finally
have a worthy adversary!
[CELL growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[thinking] Now
I'll know for certain
if I'm as strong
as my ancestors.
[TRUNKS] I will not
let this happen!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[yelling]
What is going on down there?!
Why in the world is
the whole planet shaking?!
It's Cell. He's
responsible for this.
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
[DENDE] Honorable Elder!
Honorable Elder!
Ah, Dende. You have
sensed it as well.
Yes! But who could be
behind such a power?!
This is the most terrible
energy that I've ever felt!
[NAMEK ELDER]
I do not know, my son.
But from the sheer
magnitude of this vile energy,
it may not only
destroy planet Earth,
but the entire universe as well!
[DENDE gasps]
[DENDE] The entire universe?!
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
[thinking] This is all my fault
because I destroyed
that stupid remote!
[NARRATOR] It looks like Cell
has finally succeeded in
reaching the
pinnacle of his power.
How will our heroes face
up against this ultimate foe?
Are the Nameks right?
Is the entire universe at risk?
FInd out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!