[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Stage Three was in full swing
as Super Saiyan Gohan
matched strength
and wits with Dabura,
Lord of the Demon World!
[DABURA]
Wha--?!
[GOHAN grunts]
[NARRATOR]
It was a brutal contest!
Fist to fist! Blow for blow!
Each warrior on a relentless
quest for victory!
[NARRATOR] A win for
Gohan would mean the end
of Babidi's plans to
resurrect the evil Majin Buu!
But does the young Super Saiyan
have the power necessary
to defeat the mighty Dabura?
Vegeta didn't think so!
But Gohan wasn't
about to give up,
even though the odds seemed
decidedly against him!
[NARRATOR] But just as
fast as Babidi could say:
[BABIDI]
Papparapa!
[NARRATOR]
The fight was over!
After perceiving the latent
evil in Vegeta's heart,
the cunning Dabura immediately
formulated a new strategy!
To bring Vegeta over
to the dark side
and let him do the dirty work!
[BABIDI cackles]
[GOHAN]
Well, what now?
[SUPREME KAI]
I don't know!
I don't understand
what's going on!
Dabura is Babidi's
greatest fighter!
It doesn't make sense that he
would withdraw from the fight!
They don't have
anyone after him!
He's their best!
[GOKU]
He mentioned a new recruit.
Do you think he was bluffing?
[SUPREME KAI]
I'm not sure.
But it seems unlikely that
a fighter of that caliber
would just drop into their
laps at a time like this!
Yeah! They're definitely
up to something!
But what?
[VEGETA] Agh. This whole thing
would be over with right now
if it wasn't for you!
[VEGETA]
I hope you're proud of yourself!
Whatd'ya mean?
I mean you disgraced us with
your pitiful performance!
There's no excuse for you
fighting the way you did!
You have Saiyan blood
running through your veins!
A warrior like Dabura
should be dead!
And now you're sitting here,
scratching your head!
Wondering what's next when it
should already be finished!
You are pitiful!
Fighting with that soft,
righteous look on your face!
It's brute strength
that determines the outcome
of a battle, not goodness!
The mightiest survive
and the weak perish!
You Piccolo and Krillin
were turned to stone!
[gasps]
That's because
they're weaklings!
Is that the kind of fate
you want for yourself?
Garden statues!
If they're lucky someone will
make a birdbath out of them!
[GOHAN thinking]
Maybe Vegeta's right!
If he'd fought Dabura he
might've destroyed him!
Then Krillin and Piccolo
would be restored
back to their normal selves!
Ohhh... What have I done?!
Hey, look, Gohan didn't
know that Dabura
was gonna run off!
I'm sure he would've
wanted one of us
to fight him if he knew!
[VEGETA] Oh, yes!
Now there's a pleasant excuse!
You're as soft
as he is, Kakarot!
And I'm tired
of playing around!
I'm going to put an end to
this thing, once and for all!
[GOKU]
Vegeta, what are you doing?!
No more weak-hearted
excuses, Kakarot!
I'm taking control
of this operation, now!
And for starters I'm going to
blow this ship to kingdom come!
[GOKU] Wait! That might do
us more harm than good!
[SUPREME KAI]
Goku's right!
If you blow up the ship now,
you'll most certainly
revive Buu,
Vegeta! Listen! Please!
You don't know Buu.
His power is horrible!
He's pure evil!
Not even the four Kai's
combined could stop him!
He's murdered millions
of innocent people!
Shut up!
[SUPREME KAI]
Don't be a fool!
If Buu's revived, this
planet's finished! History!
All living things
will be exterminated.
He'll turn the Earth into
a dark, lifeless tomb!
Enough!
[VEGETA]
Now you listen to me!
What happens to this planet
is none of my concern!
The strongest will
find a way to survive!
And the weaklings shall perish!
What kind of person are you?!
[GOKU] Hey! Cut it out!
This has gone far enough!
How dare you!
You better let go
of me, Kakarot!
[GOKU]
Come on!
Let's put what's
happened behind us
and move forward from here!
[VEGETA] All right!
Whatever you say, Kakarot!
Now, what I wanna know
is why they withdrew
from the fight!
Yes! It doesn't
make sense, does it?
It was the perfect opportunity!
They could've gathered
more energy.
Maybe Dabura wasn't bluffing.
Maybe they did
find a new recruit.
It's definitely a possibility.
But I don't see how.
Happening upon someone
that could beat us all...
What are the chances
of doing that?
Slim to none, I'd say!
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
Perhaps the "perfect warrior"
that Dabura was speaking
of is right here among us!
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Oh, no! Don't tell me...!
He's the one!
[BABIDI cackles]
[BABIDI] Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
I love it! I love it!
This is too good to be true!
[cackles]
[DABURA] I take it that
you are pleased, master.
[BABIDI]
Oh, yes! Immensely so!
What a great discovery
you have made, Dabura!
This one is nothing
like the others!
Yes! You hit the nail
right on the head!
What a beautiful, arrogant,
selfish piece of work!
Yes!
Oh, my! Look how uptight he is!
[cackles]
Yes! He is a rare find, indeed!
Can you imagine the
energy he'll create
when he turns on the others?
Resurrecting Buu
will be oh, so easy...
[cackles] All right!
What are we waiting for?
Let's do it!
[BABIDI grunting]
[BABIDI yelling, grunting]
[DABURA grunts]
[yelling]
[gasps]
[VEGETA grunting]
Huh? Vegeta! Hey, what's wrong?
[GOKU, SUPREME KAI gasp]
[screams]
[GOKU]
Vegeta! What's going on?!
[VEGETA]
Something's... attacking... me!
[GOKU]
Where?! We can't see anything!
[VEGETA]
Inside!
Fight it! Resist!
[VEGETA]
I... can't!
[SUPREME KAI]
You must!
[screams]
[SUPREME KAI]
That's it! Resist!
[VEGETA grunting, yelling]
[GOKU, GOHAN gasp]
[SUPREME KAI]
Don't let him win, Vegeta!
Don't let him do it!
That's it! Fight! Fight it!
Supreme Kai!
What's happening to him?
Vegeta, no! Don't let him!
You've changed!
You're not that way any more!
Babidi has no claim over you!
What's Babidi doing?
Trying to kill him?
Worse than that!
He's trying to take over
his mind and enslave him
so that he'll do whatever
Babidi wishes him to do!
[GOHAN] Isn't there any
way that we can help him?
[SUPREME KAI] He struggles
because his heart is impure!
He has to choose himself!
Don't let him take you, Vegeta!
Let go! The past is the past!
Don't think of it!
Be innocent and clear!
How can you say that...?
I'm not innocent!
I'm afraid it's too late. Yes!
You belong to us, now!
Now, allow me to
restore your power
to the way it was before
you began trying to resist
your dark nature!
[BABIDI yelling]
[VEGETA yelling, grunting]
[gasps] Whoa! No way!
[GOHAN]
Don't let them do it, Vegeta!
Don't let them use you!
You're stronger than they--
[GOHAN yelps]
[GOKU]
Gohan! Are you okay?!
Yeah. I'm fine.
[VEGETA yelling]
[GOKU]
Vegeta! No!
[SUPREME KAI]
Huh?
[GOHAN]
Fight it, Vegeta!
[VEGETA grunting, yelling]
[VEGETA yelling]
[GOKU, SUPREME KAI grunt]
What a monsterous
power! It's terrible!
I can't even approach it!
[cackles]
[yells]
[VEGETA groans]
Dad, talk to him!
Vegeta! We're here. It's okay.
We're going to help
you get back to normal!
No! Stop!
[BOTH gasp]
It's too late!
Hmm.
No! Vegeta...
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA laughing]
[CROWD cheering]
[yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER]
Yes! Yes!
Our beloved champion for
another year, Mister Satan!
I am the strongest
man alive! Oh yeah!
All right! Mister Satan!
You rock!
Yay! We love you!
[yells]
[MR. SATAN] I am the greatest
fighter in the world!
And nobody can stop me!
[yells]
[MR. SATAN]
I am the untouchable champion
that can never be defeated!
[yells]
[MR. SATAN] I am the magnificent
king of the Martial Arts!
[LADIES cheering]
Yeah!
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[ATTENDANT 2]
Hey, Get back to your seat!
Come on, now! I mean it!
I don't get paid
enough for this!
Get back to your seat!
[VEGETA laughs]
Vegeta!
Look at his head!
It has an M on it like Dabura's!
[SUPREME KAI]
It's Babidi's insignia!
Vegeta is the new recruit that
Dabura was talking about!
[GOKU] Are you saying that
Vegeta's against us now?
[SUPREME KAI]
That's exactly what I'm saying.
[SUPREME KAI, GOHAN, GOKU gasp]
[BABIDI cackles] Oh, my!
This is going to be good!
Ah, haa! But they need a more
interesting place to fight!
Papparapa!
Great! What now?
It looks like Babidi's decided
to transport us again...
[CROWD cheering]
Hey! We're back!
He sent us to the
Martial Arts stadium!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
Huh?
Wow!
How'd they do that, Eugene?!
I don't know! Beats me, man!
Goku! What's going on?!
How did they just
appear there like that?!
Instant Transmission maybe?
[YAMCHA]
No!
They have to be
touching Goku for that!
[CHICHI laughs]
They're back! Thank goodness!
[BULMA]
Vegeta!
Great! There goes
our prize money!
Nothing ever changes
with those two!
They never earn a dime!
And as always, they're late!
Hey, wait!
Maybe they could still
get some prize money
if they knocked Mr. Satan out
in front of all these people!
It doesn't work that way!
Hush up!
Goku and Gohan beat Cell and
that bum got rich off it!
Now tell me, is that fair?!
No! But that's the
way it goes, Chichi!
Hey, guys! Take a look!
Something's seriously
wrong here!
[YAMCHA, CHICHI, BULMA, PUAR]
Huh?
[ANNOUNCER]
Excuse me, gentlemen!
The championship has
already been concluded!
You all look very strong,
but there's always next year!
[VEGETA] We're just here for
a little exhibition match!
Ahh!
Goku! I didn't see you
back there! Welcome!
I'm afraid you and your friends
have arrived a little too late!
[VEGETA]
Huh?
Look out!
[yelps]
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[yells]
[MR. SATAN grunting]
[cackles]
[BABIDI]
Now what shall I have him do?
Let's see! Hm! Oh, yes!
I know! Of course!
[cackles]
Vegeta, this is your new
master, Babidi, speaking!
It's time for you
to have a little fun!
You can start by
killing your friends!
I won't...!
My goal is to fight Kakarot...!
The... The others are nothing!
Vegeta! How could you?
Wow! This guy's something else!
Even after all that, he's still
not completely under my control!
But he'll come
around eventually!
Yes! I know you will! Won't you?
It almost looked like
Vegeta attacked the others!
--Did he?
--I think he just powered up.
But he is being a bit cocky.
[ROSHI]
Vegeta is different somehow.
[MR. SATAN whimpering] I can't
believe that they're back!
Wh-What if they come after me?
What am I gonna do?
[MR. SATAN whimpering]
[VEGETA]
It's time, Kakarot.
Vegeta! No!
[VEGETA cackles]
[gasps]
Oh, no!
[ANNOUNCER whimpering]
[GOKU grunting]
[yelling]
[GOKU yelps]
No!
Look out!
[CROWD screams]
[GOHAN, ANNOUNCER gasping]
[gasps]
[GOHAN gasps]
[CHICHI, ROSHI gasping]
Ohh, Vegeta!
[VEGETA cackles]
No! How could he?
This is... too awful.
There must be some mistake!
[YAMCHA, PUAR gasp]
[CROWD screaming]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Shame on you!
The Vegeta I know would
never have done this!
[NARRATOR] After many years,
Vegeta is once again
challenging Goku to
mortal combat on Earth!
Can the possessed Prince
chase out the demons
that Babidi has let
loose in his head?
Or will disaster
strike once again!
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!