[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
the beauty of Mother
Earth was overtaken
by the Black Water Mist.
A fog of evil that was
released from Kami's Lookout
by Garlic Jr., who had turned
the once magnificent sanctuary
into a den of corruption!
[NARRATOR] As Garlic Jr.
swore an oath of darkness
to use the Dragon Balls
to restore his father,
Garlic, back to life,
the Black Water Mist
continued to spread below
and exercise
it's mysterious power
over all who breathed it!
Sweet, timid animals became
ravenous and blood-thirsty.
[NARRATOR] Ordinary
housewives were turned into
murderous fiends!
[NARRATOR] Even Goku's friends,
defenders of the earth
and upholders of justice,
were transformed into
minions of evil
by the dreadful mist!
But there was
more trouble on the way.
The Spice Boys had arrived.
And they meant business.
Oh, great! Who are those goons?
[NARRATOR] Gohan went for
the head-on attack
only to be stopped in his tracks
by Garlic Jr.'s evil henchmen,
Spice, Vinegar,
Mustard, and Salt!
Piccolo.
[NARRATOR] But just as Gohan
seemed to be done for,
his Namekian ally
came to te rescue.
[GOHAN] Piccolo!
[KRILLIN] All right!
Good. Yeah, this'll be fun!
[SALT] Garlic Jr. can
destroy you anytime, Piccolo!
He has Kami
held captive, you fool!
What? Garlic Jr.'s back?
[NARRATOR] And so
Piccolo was surrounded
by an army of
darkness made up of
friends and foes alike.
What happens next? Stay tuned!
[SPICE] Admit it! You've
always had a fascination
with the dark side, Piccolo.
Why don't you join Garlic Jr.
now, while you still can?
He's about to
take over the planet.
Yeah, right.
Don't make me laugh.
C'mon! How can
someone stupid enough
to get caught in his own trap
take over a planet, friend?
[MUSTARD]
Hey! Watch your mouth!
[SALT] You're going to wish you
never said that, lizard boy!
Yikes! Get ready, Gohan!
[KRILLIN] We're gonna
have to move in fast!
Are you nuts?
You can't leave me
here by myself!
You're supposed to protect me
from danger, Krillin!
No! Please! Don't go!
Hush up, Maron!
[VINEGAR] You're lucky that
Lord Garlic ordered us
to take you in alive, or I'd
finish you off right now!
How did your brainless boss
escape the Dead Zone?
All right, that's it!
You're dead!
Hey...
[chuckles]
Settle down, Vinegar.
[SPICE] He's just trying
to get you riled up.
[SPICE] I'll answer
your question, Piccolo,
if you really want to know.
The power of the Makyo Star.
Go on. How?
Ah, yes! Now I have
your attention.
Not long ago
the autumnal equinox was
[SPICE] on the first
point of Libra.
Heralding this auspicious
moment for the dark side
was the Makyo Star,
whose proximity
to the earth provided
an incredible source of power
to all creatures of the night.
This rare alignment
of the planets and stars
occurs only once
every 12,000 years.
At no other time
is man more susceptible
to evil than this.
It is a time when
the powers of darkness
are at their zenith,
and the unseen lower
forces dominate the earth.
Garlic Jr. used this
influx of dark energy
as a springboard
to shatter his prison
and escape it forever.
[chuckles]
[SPICE]
You don't get it, do you?
Garlic Jr. is the new
guardian of the earth.
He's taken over Kami's
Lookout and is seated
quite comfortably on the throne.
Kami and Popo are
just mantle pieces now,
looking on helplessly
from the little glass jars.
Huh?!
Great! We're in trouble!
[SPICE] The beautiful part
about it all is that with
the Black Water Mist, we hardly
have to raise a finger.
Just look how eager
your friends are to help us.
We're gods to these plebeians!
We're like celebrities
to all these people!
Kinda like their
role models and all!
Yeah! Dig it, man!
You should join us.
You would love it.
They worship us!
And soon they're gonna
be like that for good!
--[GOHAN] Huh?
--[KRILLIN] What? For good?
Once twenty-four
hours passes by,
the change becomes permanent!
Not even the Sacred Water
can change them back!
[chuckles]
You came here
looking to fight us,
but the battle
has already been won.
There's no one left
to fight for.
Nobody wants your help.
Can't you understand that?
Just look!
Look at your friends!
[SPICE] Do they look like
they're waiting for
a knight in shining armor
to come and rescue them?
[SPICE] Who do you think
you're fooling, anyway?
You haven't really changed.
So drop the goody-two-shoes act
and join us. Or, oppose us...
...and suffer like you've
never suffered before.
Your choice.
Well?
[chuckles]
Huh?
Why you louse!
So that's your choice.
That's it! I've had
enough of this, jerk!
[VINEGAR]
You're gonna get it now!
Well, we'll see.
[VINEGAR chuckles]
Man! If that
was your best shot,
you're in big trouble,
my friend!
[PICCOLO groans]
[chuckles]
Yamcha! Stop it!
Stop it, guys! Yamcha!
Hey, what's the deal, Krillin?
You said you were an expert!
You can't even beat
an old man! Some expert!
But, he's better than he looks!
[yells]
Oh, man! Krillin?
[MARON screams]
Now what?
[chuckles]
[MARON] Forget this!
[MARON yelps]
No! And I thought I'd been
to weird beach parties before!
Darling!
[ROSHI] Yes, honey?
[laughs]
[MARON] Krillin! Help me!
[yells]
[screams]
Maron! No!
All right! You rule, Icarus!
[KRILLIN] Take good
care of her, okay?
Krillin!
Look! He can't even
keep up with his friends,
nevermind us!
Don't Piccolo, please!
Move it!
[screeches]
Oh my gosh!
Tell me what to do! Hurry!
All right!
You take off! Now! Got it?
Huh?
The whole planet's
been infected,
just like Yamcha and your mom!
You need to get
the Sacred Water!
Yeah! But you...
Hey! He knows
what he's doing, Gohan!
Leave! Get the water!
But be careful--
Garlic Jr.'s going to be
up there guarding it!
[chuckles]
Do it!
Right! We'll be back!
[PICCOLO] The Yamcha I know
would tear you apart!
[PICCOLO] I'm sorry,
but you leave me no choice.
I'm going to have
to exterminate you all!
I hate to do this.
[grunts]
It's not your fault.
[PICCOLO] Huh? What?
[groans]
[growls]
[yells]
Huh? Piccolo!
[groans]
[BOTH yell]
[yells]
Oh, my goodness!
[PICCOLO] Gohan, no!
[grunts, yells]
[PICCOLO] Gohan...
Do as I said! Now!
[GOHAN]
I won't leave you, Piccolo!
Gohan...! Now!
That runt! Should I?
No, stay.
I'm sure that he's
after the Sacred Water.
He won't get far.
Yeah, that's it. Go, kid.
[YAMCHA yells]
[BOTH chuckle]
[BOTH chuckle lightly]
Must... hold on...
[groans]
Hey!
[GOHAN] Huh? Krillin!
Yeah! Let's rock!
Right!
[MARON] Hey Krillin!
Huh? Auh...
Wait up! I'm coming with you!
Oh no you're not!
Maron, this is serious!
You'd be in real danger!
So what? I don't care!
I'm still coming!
Huh?
Good! Case closed!
Where are we going, guys? Huh?
Maron. That's very
brave of you,
but this is no
place for a girl.
All right. But if you
make me leave now,
then I'm not gonna be
your girlfriend anymore!
You're not?
That's right! Forget it!
It's all over!
Unless I can
come with you! Hmph!
[MARON] Well?
Oh, man!
Oh... all right. I guess!
Huh? Yay!
If things heat up,
take a B-line outta there.
[giggles]
You are such a stud! Mwah!
[sighs]
[GARLIC JR.] Yes, yes. Come to
me, Gohan. I'm waiting!
[chuckles]
[SPICE]
His Namek body is having
a strong reaction to the venom.
Too bad. Let's put him
out of his misery.
Vinegar, stop.
Huh?
We mustn't kill poor Piccolo.
Without him, we won't be able
to use the Dragon Balls.
[VINEGAR] Do I get to
kill him later then?
'Fraid not.
Huh?
Why should we hurt a friend?
If you're bitten
by someone who's been
[SPICE] infected by
the Black Water Mist,
you become just like them.
[laughs wheezingly]
[SPICE]
Piccolo's one of us.
Yes. Wake up.
You're part of the family now.
[snarls]
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere...
deep in space...
a certain Saiyan Prince
has been a most
unwelcome guest
on a strange planet!
My word! So this is
what my people get
for being loyal
servants to Frieza?
How could he order
Vegeta to do this to us
[WARRIOR]
after all we've done for him?
[VEGETA] Fool! No one
tells me what to do anymore!
Especially Frieza!
[WARRIOR]
You dare to defy Frieza?
Look! I did not come here
to fight with you!
It was you and your
idiotic friends
that started it
in the first place.
Now tell me where Goku is!
I've never even heard of him!
[VEGETA] If you're lying to me,
I will rip your head off!
Heh! We're protected
under Frieza's treaty.
You're the one
who's going to get it.
Really? Is that so?
[yells]
The treaty you signed with
Frieza is no longer valid.
Because in order for
a treaty to exist,
the one who signed it must
be alive, and Frieza's dead!
A Saiyan by the name of
Goku destroyed him.
Frieza killed by a...
a monkey! What a joke!
[chuckles]
I don't remember
telling a joke, bird-face!
Aah...!
[VEGETA] You just made my day!
[grunts]
[VEGETA] I don't know
where you are, Kakarot,
but I am going to find you!
You're around here somewhere.
I can feel it!
I have to know
how you did it, Kakarot!
I need to be a Super Saiyan!
[KRILLIN] Gosh! I don't know,
Gohan. What d'ya think?
[GOHAN] I don't know either!
What do you think?
[KRILLIN] Well, if Korin
got a whiff of that mist,
this is the last place
on Earth that I'd want to be!
Hey! What's the deal?
[BOTH] Shh!
[KRILLIN] Maron, be quiet!
Man! Sorry, Gohan.
Let's move in. Ready?
Yeah!
It's so cold! I'm freezing!
[MARON]
Can you guys get me a--
[BOTH] Shh!
Hey! What's the problem, guys?
[MARON]
Nobody's even around!
Krillin, there!
Huh?
[distant clanking]
Oh, hey! What's shakin'?
Yo, dudes! What's goin' on?
Hi, guys!
Boy, are we glad to see you two.
It's nice to see you, too.
But you woke me up from a nap.
[giggles]
What a cute little cat!
Ahh! Huh?
[moans lightly]
That's enough!
Whoa! My word! Who is this girl?
Uhh, Maron.
Now look here! This is a holy
place! Not a beach hang-out!
Uh, yes, sir.
Maron is Krillin's
new girlfriend. Heh!
Oh, really?
Yes, sir. [laughs nervously]
For now!
All right! How did
a dog-ugly guy like you
score that chick?
Hey, cool it on the ugly stuff!
Now what's up, you guys?
So, how can I help you today?
[GOHAN] Oh, yeah! Gosh!
I don't know where to begin!
It's crazy down there!
Just calm down!
It'll be easier if I just
read your thoughts!
Oh!
Yowza! This is terrible!
So, you're heading
to Kami's to get
the Sacred Water, are you?
Uh huh!
Boy, that's not
going to be easy.
Garlic Jr.'s not stupid.
He'll be watching like a hawk.
Eh, so, you guys,
it's vital that you get there
before the others warn him.
Time is absolutely of
the essence in this endeavor.
[KORIN]
Ah, hey! You're leaving?!
Time is of the essence, Korin!
Take care of Maron!
[KORIN] Wait a second,
this isn't fair!
[MARON] Krillin, you said
I could come with you!
You guys can't do this to me.
Get back here right now!
Huh?
[MARON] You're so cute!
Will you stop that? Heavens!
[KRILLIN] Look how
trashed this place is!
Mr. Popo would have a
heart attack if he saw this.
[GOHAN] It's creepy, isn't it?
[KRILLIN] Yeah...
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
So you don't like
the new decor, aye?
Well, what do you two know?
You little do-good punks!
[laughs]
So you want the Sacred Water?
Well come and get it!
Gohan!
Right!
[BOTH yell]
Piccolo! Yeah!
Gohan! He's not normal!
[KRILLIN] He's been
infected by the mist!
[growls]
[GOHAN] Piccolo!
What took you two so long?
We've been waiting
for you! So has he!
Man!
Ugh! This isn't looking good!
[chuckles]
[growls]
[NARRATOR] With Piccolo now
under the control of the mist,
how will Gohan and Krillin
fight this battle?
On the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!