[NARRATOR] On the last episode
of Dragon Ball Z,
it was Majin verses
Saiyan, as the battle
that would decide the fate
of the Universe raged on.
[NARRATOR]
It was a trial of pain for Goku,
but the darker it got,
the brighter his light shined.
And in classic style,
he countered Buu's every attack.
[NARRATOR]
But as the battle wore on,
Goku felt the power needed to
destroy Buu slipping away.
[GOKU growls]
I should have done it.
Darn it, now I'm weak.
I'll need time.
I havee got it covered,
Kakarot. Sixty seconds.
Get what you need,
and finish him off.
[NARRATOR]
One minute.
That's how long Vegeta
had to keep Buu occupied
so Goku could gather the
energy needed to destroy him.
But in this fight, one minute
can seem an eternity.
Has the Saiyan Prince
reached the end of his rope?
Stay tuned to find out.
[gasps]
What's going on?
I should have been able
to gather all the energy
I need by now.
[VEGETA screams]
[groaning]
[laughs]
--[KID BUU laughing]
--[VEGETA gasping]
Vegeta!
[VEGETA groaning]
--[KID BUU grunts]
--[VEGETA screaming]
[laughing]
[VEGETA screaming]
--[KID BUU laughs]
--[VEGETA groaning]
[VEGETA yells]
[groans]
[KID BUU chuckles]
[VEGETA groans]
--[KID BUU laughs]
--[VEGETA groans]
[OLD KIA] I know it's
difficult to watch, son,
but you can't leave now.
[KABITO KAI] It's not that, Sir.
I've decided to go home.
What? Are you crazy?
I know Buu's strength is
vastly superior to my own,
that fact has been proven
on more than one occasion,
but I think I can at
least stand up to him
long enough to give
Goku a little extra time.
I can't stand by and watch again
like I did all those years ago,
when Majin Buu first
attacked my fellow Kais.
Even if I can only
buy one extra second,
it'll be worth it.
[OLD KAI]
Wait a minute.
[DENDE]
Yeah, wait. I'm coming, too.
Uh? You, too?
I'm no fighter,
but if I can manage
to stay alive,
my healing powers
might come in handy.
Are you sure?
[DENDE]
Yes, sir. I'm positive.
I'm willing to take the chance
if it means helping Goku. Hm.
Outstanding.
Well, shall we go?
Right.
Hold it! Hold it!
--[OLD KAI panting]
--[DENDE, KABITO KAI] Hm?
[OLD KAI panting]
Just a second. Not so fast.
Look, I know you both
want to help,
and I very much
admire your courage,
but if you show up now
that's just two more people
Goku has to worry about.
Please, don't go yet.
I know how you must feel,
but we have to trust
in Goku's judgment.
Let's be patient, and let
him and Vegeta handle this.
I still believe those two
know what they're doing.
It's hard to watch them suffer,
but you have to realize that
this is what they live for.
[VEGETA screaming]
[laughing]
[groaning]
[GOKU thinking]
Vegeta...
[VEGETA gasps]
[laughing]
[VEGETA groans]
Oh, no.
[GOKU thinking]
Incredible.
He's getting up again.
[panting]
Kakarot, go, it's my fault
I'm in this pitiful state now,
not yours.
Now finish the job you started!
[GOKU gasps]
[KID BUU laughs]
Ah!
--[KID BUU screams]
--[VEGETA choking]
Not good.
If Vegeta gets hit by an energy
blast of that magnitude,
he's a goner.
[choking]
[laughs]
I can't let this happen.
[MR. SATAN]
Buu!
[gasps]
[KID BUU]
Hm?
Caught you with your filthy
hand in the cookie jar,
didn't I, big guy?
How long did you think
you could get away
with these injustices?
Mr. Satan will step in
if that other coward won't.
[grunting]
You know the real
battle's about to begin.
So laugh while you can,
'cause I'm gonna pound
that smile offa your face.
[chuckles]
Please. Not him.
What did I do to deserve this?
[VEGETA groans]
[MR. SATAN] You had your
way with those other two,
but let's see how you do
against the World Champion!
[MR. SATAN]
Kiss my blarney stone.
[MR. SATAN] What's the matter?
Is Buu scared of the Champ?
Aw. Poor Buu-buu.
[MR. SATAN thinking]
Maybe this nightmare
is gonna turn into a
Mr. Satan saves
the Universe dream!
[growls]
On guard, you.
[KID BUU yells]
--[KID BUU yells]
--[MR. SATAN gasps]
That doesn't sound too good.
[screams, gasps]
[MR. SATAN]
Please, don't hurt me.
I was only kidding before,
when I said that stuff about
you being scared of me.
Really, I didn't mean any of it!
Please.
Amazing. He's got it
down to an art form.
[laughs] What style!
And it's working.
[MR. SATAN]
Please!
[growling]
[screams]
[MR. SATAN]
Please don't hurt me.
I'm begging you, Buu.
For old time's sake.
[chuckles]
Huh?!
[screaming]
Hey, what's up? Aren't
you gonna kill me?
[KID BUU screaming]
Hey, I know now,
he must be sensing my aura.
[laughs]
Ha! Take that,
it serves ya right.
--[MR. SATAN laughing]
--[KID BUU screaming]
Feel my power.
--[KID BUU groaning]
--[MR. SATAN laughing]
Over here. Made you look.
Yoo-hoo. Too much speed, huh?
[GOKU thinking]
This is bizarre.
He has Buu completely subdued,
but he doesn't seem
to be doing anything.
[VEGETA]
Kakarot.
What are you doing?
Idiot. You should use
this time to power up.
Aw, man. You're right.
[yells]
Yeah. Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Now you know what true power is.
[gasps]
B-Buu?!
[laughing]
[OLD KAI]
My word.
Double Buu's?!
[OLD KAI] Can either of you
tell me what's going on?
Well, sort of.
I know the original Majin Buu
was friends with Mister Satan,
until he split and was absorbed
by the newer, evil form.
He must've still been
inside evil Buu's body,
and he kept him
from harming Mr. Satan.
So the evil Buu
spit the good Buu out
like a piece of
used-up chewing gum.
That means he'll
attack Mr. Satan now,
but I guess it doesn't
really matter at this point.
I don't know. He has
a few serious character flaws,
that's for sure,
but as fate would have it,
he's the last human alive.
You see, the sole survivor.
[KID BUU panting]
[MR. SATAN gasps]
Buu!
Buu. Ar-Are you all right?
Say somethin', please.
It's me. Your old pal.
[BEE whines]
Buu.
You saved me again, didn't you?
You kept him from attacking me.
[cries] Please, Buu.
You're the only friend I have.
[MR. SATAN]
It can't end like this.
I-I won't let it end like this.
That does it.
He's through. No more!
[grunts] Hey, you.
You're finished.
It's over. I'm gonna
tear you limb from limb.
[chuckles]
What? You don't think I can?
Well guess again, fool.
Don't you realize
what you're up against?
You are walkin' towards
your own doom!
[KID BUU laughs]
Fine. So be it.
You missed your chance
to turn around, buddy.
It's time to face the master!
--[MR. SATAN grunts]
--[KID BUU laughs]
[MR. SATAN thinking]
He's acting like he's not scared
of me again. My aura
must be calm right now.
[grunting]
[gasping]
Go ahead, take a knee,
Buu. I know it hurt.
[KID BUU laughs]
[MR. SATAN groans]
[MR. SATAN]
Not the nose. N-Not the nose!
You've just defaced
a national monument.
--[BEE barking]
--[MR. SATAN groaning]
[laughing]
[MR. SATAN]
All right, you scoundrel.
I'll give you one last chance.
If you don't want to be
destroyed, then surrender now.
Or, at least, apologize.
[laughs, whoops]
Well, I guess that's how
your kind says I'm sorry.
Uh, granted, it's a bit
primitive and unusual, but hey.
No hard feelings.
Apology accept--
[KID BUU grunts]
[gasps]
He's alive.
[gasping]
[BEE barks]
[BUU]
Bee! Mmm! [laughs]
[gasps]
B-Buu?
[growls]
You leave alone!
Him Buu's buddy.
Buu. You're alive!
Thank goodness.
[VEGETA grunting]
Kakarot, hurry up! How long
is this going to take?
Something's not right.
It's not working. I don't' know.
I was almost up to
full power a minute ago,
but then it just started
slipping away.
What? What do you mean?
[growls]
[KID BUU]
Huh?!
[gasps]
[KID BUU laughs]
[screams]
--[BUU laughs]
--[KID BUU growls]
What a golden opportunity.
Come on, Kakarot.
It doesn't get much
better than this.
[VEGETA] What are you
doing up there? Come on!
Something's wrong. Come on.
What's going on?
I just can't concentrate.
I need to relax, let go.
I'm way too tense.
No, you're kidding me.
[DENDE gasps]
This can't be.
[BUU screams]
[gasps]
[MR. SATAN]
B-B-Buu. Oh, no!
[laughing]
Buu.
Yeah. That's it.
Put it on tight.
Yeah, you're the one. Kick his
scrawny little behind, Buu.
[laughing, growls]
Me big Buu. Why little
Buu stronger? Hm.
[MR. SATAN]
Yeah. Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Give it to him, Buu. Whooo!
Ha. I can't believe that moron's
done something useful.
[gasping]
[NARRATOR] It's high noon on
the sacred world of the Kais,
as the showdown between
the Buu's is about to begin.
But how long can the goodly Buu
manage to stave off
his evil counterpart?
And with Goku losing
power instead of gaining,
is there any real
hope for success?
Stay tuned!