[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Faced with the terror of
Frieza and his evil henchmen,
three brave Namekian
warriors stepped up
to meet
the challenge!
[NARRATOR] Though
heavily outnumbered,
the Nameks launched into
battle with all their might...
Stunning
Frieza's men
with their unexpected
show of power.
[NARRATOR] The Nameks moved
with lightning speed
and with their superior
strength and agility,
their enemies found
themselves chasing shadows,
unable to land
a single blow.
And for a time, it seemed
the forces of good
would win the day...
Raaugh!
[yelling]
Go! Go! Go!
Atta way!
[NARRATOR] But the scene took
a sudden turn for the worse,
as Frieza ordered his
lieutenant Dodoria
to put an end to the
Namek resistance...
[DODORIA] So do you just want me
to kill one as an example?
[FRIEZA] Kill them all.
[NARRATOR]
That's when the Namek Elder
made a bold,
and desperate move!
The scouters!
I should have known.
That's what
he's aiming for!
[thinking]
That crafty old dog.
Uh, wait a second.
Why is he just
destroying the scouters?
Think about it!
Without the scouters,
Frieza and his men
won't be able to find the
Nameks or the Dragon Balls!
Even if Frieza gets the Dragon
Ball he's looking for here,
he's gonna have
a heck of a time
tracking down the next one.
You gotta admire him.
He's risking everything
to protect his people!
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
the Elder's bravery
in the face of danger
only served to incur
Dodoria's wrath...
[DODORIA] You think you're
pretty smart, don't you?!
But you're not!
I'll kill
all you Nameks!
[DODORIA] And I'm
gonna start with you!
[DODORIA yells]
[NARRATOR] Dodoria attacks!
Today, on Dragon Ball Z!
Raaugh!
[NAMEKS gasping]
[GOHAN and KRILLIN gasping]
[ELDER NAMEK grunting]
Elder!
Dodoria!
Not yet!
[FRIEZA] I want
you to eliminate
these three young
warriors first!
[DODORIA yells]
[DODORIA chuckles menacingly]
[DODORIA]
All right.
A little appetizer
before the main course.
[DODORIA chuckling]
[DODORIA] Now, which one of
you pathetic weaklings
wants to be
first to die?
[NAMEK 1] Don't be ridiculous.
There's three of us!
We have you
outnumbered.
Oh? Don't think you'll
find safety in numbers.
I can take on
twelve of you.
Huh?!
Waaugh!
[NAMEK 2 growling]
Raaah!
Taah!
[NAMEK 2 screaming]
[DODORIA chuckles]
[NAMEKIAN CHILDREN whimpering]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN gasping]
[NAMEK 3 growling]
[growling]
Raaah!
[BOTH gasping]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[DODORIA coughs, chuckles]
Nooo!
You're kidding! That didn't
even faze him?! Come on!
[DODORIA yelling]
[NAMEK 3 screams]
[yelling continues]
[NAMEK 3 shouting]
[MOORI gasps]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN gasping]
[DODORIA chuckling]
[FRIEZA] Heh, heh...
So, do you
finally understand?
As I've tried to explain
to you from the start,
it is impossible for
you to defeat us.
Now, give me
the Dragon Ball!
[MOORI growls]
[FRIEZA] Good. You
can trust me when I say
you've made the
right decision.
And since you owe us
something in return
for destroying
our scouters,
I think this is more
than an equitable trade,
don't you agree?
[NAMEKIAN CHILDREN whimpering]
You wretch...
You leave me no choice.
Just promise me you'll
leave us in peace!
[ZARBON] Hmph.
[FRIEZA] Oh,
and don't worry
I'll keep an eye on the
children until you get back.
[KRILLIN] Rrgh... You got what
you wanted. Enough already!
[GOHAN growling]
I hate him!
Calm down, Gohan. I told you,
we're just gonna have to wait.
I don't like
it either,
but we aren't gonna do any good
by getting ourselves killed!
[GOHAN growling]
[GOKU grunting]
Huh?
[GOKU squealing]
Wah!
[GOKU grunts]
Oww!
Wow, whoever said
"no pain, no gain"
definitely wasn't
kidding! Ow!
Here, now you have what you
came for. Take it and leave!
[FRIEZA] I'll do that.
[FRIEZA] And while I'm deciding
whether or not to kill you,
tell me where to find
the last two Dragon Balls!
How dare you!
We had an agreement!
Take your Dragon Ball
and leave us as promised!
You'll get nothing
more from me!
[FRIEZA] Hmph.
Go. For the last time,
go now, and leave us in peace!
Oh, shut up.
I promised nothing.
And considering
the circumstances,
I'd hardly say
you're in a position
to be issuing
threats.
Now, tell me what
I want to know,
or I'll beat
it out of you!
How dare you!
Do your worst!
[growling]
Uugh!
[NAMEKIAN CHILDREN]
Oh, no! Elder!
You monster!
What have you done?!
You can torture
me all you'd like.
It won't do you any good!
I don't know where they are!
One: You're lying.
And two: You've already
hindered my search
by destroying
the scouters.
Normally, I'd say that's
more than enough reason
to kill you.
But I'm feeling generous.
I'll give you one last
chance to save yourself.
[MOORI] And why
should I trust you?
Why should I believe
the word of a murderer?
[FRIEZA giggles]
Oh well, I guess
you caught me.
I was planning to kill
you even if you talked.
You!
We don't need him.
Even without the scouters,
it shouldn't be too difficult
to find the next village.
Yes, Zarbon. You must
have read my mind.
[DODORIA chuckles]
Those... scumbags!
Children, listen to me.
Run and get help!
Uh-huh!
[NAMEKIAN CHILDREN whimpering]
Alright, then. If it's a
fight you want, so be it!
Raah!
Taah!
Huh...? Aah!
[GOHAN and KRILLIn gasp]
No...
Cargo!
[GOHAN growling]
Don't do it, Gohan!
[growling continues]
I'm sorry, but if
we go down there
we'll end up
just like him!
Say something! Cargo!
Oh, Cargo, please!
[DODORIA growling]
[MOORI grunts]
Uwaugh!
Aaaah!
Aah!
[whimpering]
[FRIEZA giggles]
Ha, ha, ha...
That's two Nameks down,
and one more to go.
[screams]
Ha, ha, ha!
[GOHAN growling]
[DODORIA laughs heartily]
What's wrong?
Don't you wanna play, kid?
[GOHAN growling]
[DODORIA] I do!
And I know just the thing:
Play dead!
[GOHAN screaming]
Stop it!!
[KRILLIN]
Gohan! No!
[FRIEZA] Hm?
[ZARBON] Ah!
What the...?
Who's that? Huh?
[GOHAN growling]
Huh?!
Ha! Take that, jerk!
What? Where did
you come from?
[KRILLIN] Well, here we go!
If you want him, you're
gonna have to get through me!
If you insist--
[KRILLIN] Yaah!
[GOHAN] Good one, Krillin!
C'mon, Gohan! We gotta
get outta here! Right now!
Move, Gohan!
Zarbon, make
a note, please.
I must find out who
those little rodents are.
Noted.
[DODORIA growling]
Dodoria, what
are you doing?!
Get off your fat butt
and follow them, now!
[DODORIA yelling]
[yells]
[DODORIA laughing]
Step on it,
Gohan!
If he catches us, we're
just as good as dead!
Got it!
Okay, so you want to turn
it up a notch, do you?
Oh, great! Lumpy's gaining
on us! We're in trouble!
Those two were
fairly strong.
Whoever they are, I
suspect they're the ones
who took out our
scouts earlier.
And if we're
not careful,
they could cause us even
more trouble. Perhaps--
[FRIEZA] Zarbon...
You disappoint me...
Could it be your faith in my
power is beginning to waver?
[FRIEZA chuckling]
They are just a minor
annoyance, Zarbon.
Nothing more.
[GOKU grunting]
Wah!
[GOKU squealing]
[DODORIA]
Give it up! It's no use!
You can run but there's
nowhere you can hide!
[DODORIA]
I'm gonna get you!
And when I do,
I'm going to make you pay!
And pay dearly!
[DODORIA laughing]
Ah!
[DODORIA growling]
[DODORIA] Haa!
Heads up!
[DODORIA laughing]
[DODORIA] Haa!
[DODORIA]
Haa, haa, haa, haa!
[KRILLIN] Aargh!
Uh?! Oh, no!
Ah-Aaah!
[DODORIA laughing]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN] Let go!
[DODORIA laughing]
[KRILLIN] Hyaah!
[DODORIA groaning]
I'm not
gonna make it!
[KRILLIN sighs]
Gohan! Get going!
He's closing in and fast!
Haah!
[BOTH] Huh?!
They're quick! Just makes
killing 'em all the more fun.
[GOHAN screams]
Hey, Krillin! Don't look now,
but he's right behind us!
Never mind!
Just keep going
as fast as you can!
Our only hope is if we
can outrun him somehow!
[DODORIA chuckling]
[DODORIA laughing]
Man! He's still gaining
and I'm out of ideas...
Wait! No,
I'm not! Gohan!
Listen! Whatever
happens, just keep going!
Don't look back!
I think I might have a
way to slow this guy down!
Okay!
Hmm...?
[KRILLIN grunting]
[KRILLIN] Alright,
big guy! Watch the birdie!
Solar Flaaaare!
[DODORIA grunting]
[DODORIA] My eyes! My eyes!
What have you done to my eyes?!
Whadda you know?
It actually worked!
[DODORIA] I'll get you
for this! I swear it!
[DODORIA groaning]
C'mon, Gohan! Hurry!
Now's our chance!
[groaning]
Where...
Where are they?!
If those little twerps
think they can outrun me,
they've got another
thing coming.
And when I get my
hands on them,
they're gonna lose a
lot more than their eyes!
Do you hear me?!
I'm gonna tear you apart!
I'm gonna rip
you to pieces!
And I'm gonna love
every minute of it!
[DODORIA growls frustratedly]
[KRILLIN chuckling]
That was great, Krillin!
Where'd you learn that?
Oh, uh, it's just a little
trick I picked up from Tien.
[DODORIA growling]
[growling continues]
[GOHAN] Shhh!
I thought so...
Without his scouter, he
doesn't know how to find us!
[DODORIA growling]
[NARRATOR] Have Krillin's
surprise escape tactics
actually succeeded in throwing
Dodoria off their trail?
For now,
he can only hope,
for as he has seen too
many times already,
the brunt of Dodoria's
anger can be deadly...
The tension mounts
for our heroes,
as Dodoria circles
high above.
And the slightest sound,
the smallest false step,
could bring the full
weight of his wrath
crashing down upon them!
Don't look up!
There's danger in the skies!
Next time on
Dragon Ball Z!