A gift from Korin...
One bag of Senzu Beans.
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
No more hospital
food for Goku!
Thanks to a
magic Senzu Bean,
our hero was finally able
to cast off his casts.
All you have to do is push
the button, and you're off!
That's great!
I'll definitely get there
in time to help them out!
[NARRATOR] And after
months of lying in bed,
Goku was all too eager to start
his next great adventure!
Within moments, he was
rocketing through outer space
on his way
to Planet Namek,
where his friends had
already begun their search
for the
Dragon Balls.
Meanwhile, Gohan and Krillin
were quickly realizing
they weren't the only
interested party!
[KRILLIN]
Check it out!
Look what those guys have
tucked under their arms!
It's the Dragon Balls!
[NARRATOR] Who are these
mysterious invaders?
And what does their
presence bode
for the kindly
citizens of Namek?
There's only one
way to find out...
Stay tuned for
more Dragon Ball Z!
[HENCHMAN 2] Look, Namek.
I'm about ready to put
one between your eyes
and drag you
out myself.
Got it?
Now move your feet!
[HENCHMEN laughing cruelly]
Aww, you scared?
You should be!
[KRILLIN] Those jerks!
He'd better lay off that kid.
[GOHAN] Who are these
guys, Krillin?
I mean, they're all
dressed like Vegeta!
Good question. They
wear the same uniforms,
but they're not
Saiyans... Who knows?
Maybe Vegeta really
is the only one left.
Well, that is except
for you and Goku.
But then, who?
Remember what
Goku's brother Raditz
told us when he
came to Earth?
We scour space
for planets
that will bring a high
price on the galactic market.
Once we find them, we
send our warriors there
to purge them of any life
and make them ready for sale.
My guess is, they're more
members of the planet trade.
Although, I don't see
Vegeta around anywhere.
Maybe these guys are like,
the competition or something.
[FRIEZA] I doubt I
need an introduction,
but just in case,
I am the mighty Frieza,
and yes, all the horrible
stories you've heard are true.
Now, then,
let's get right to it.
We know there were others
here with you earlier.
At least five.
And since my men and I have
much better things to do
than hunt down a
bunch of Nameks,
I wonder if you'd be so kind as
to tell us where they are.
I'm sorry.
Where are my manners?
I didn't
say "please".
[FRIEZA giggling]
[GOKU] 6,996... Whew!
This 20-times
gravity is intense!
6,997... 6,998... 6,999...
7,000!
Only 3,000 more!
7,001...
Come on, Goku...
7,00--
[FRIEZA] If you still
have any misgivings
about cooperating
with us,
I would strongly urge
you to give them up.
You see, we can do
this one of two ways.
Either you can tell
us what we want to know,
Or, we can force you to
tell us what we want to know.
And believe me,
you don't want the latter.
So, now that we
understand each other,
I think it's time
you started talking.
[DODORIA chuckles]
Nawainita hanita
emao moteleki koeto.
Hmph. Clever old fool,
don't think you can trick us
by pretending to
speak only Namek.
I know you are fluent
in the common tongue.
The elders stay in the
village with the children,
while the men go out to work
in the fields. Will that do?
[FRIEZA] That's better.
See how well we do
when you cooperate?
Now, on to the
next question.
I understand
that you have something
here in your possession
that I would very much
like to have in mine.
The Six-Star
Dragon Ball.
[GOHAN and KRILLIN gasp]
[FRIEZA] I'll give you one
chance to tell me where it is.
I... don't know what
you're talking about.
[FRIEZA giggles]
Dodoria...
Yes?
[FRIEZA] Do you remember that
first Namek elder we visited?
Doesn't our new friend here
remind you of him in some way?
Yeah, he thought he
could play dumb, too.
He said he had no idea
what the Dragon Balls were.
[DODORIA laughs]
Oh, yes, he was quite
the stubborn one at first,
but it wasn't too long
before he was willing to talk.
We simply had to start killing
his friends, one by one.
What?!
[FRIEZA] After that,
he was a regular wellspring
of useful
information.
For example, he explained
to us how long ago,
the oldest and
wisest of the Nameks
created seven
Dragon Balls.
How he placed them at different
locations all over the planet,
entrusting each one to the
care of a Namek elder.
And how, if all
seven are collected,
the Eternal
Dragon appears,
able to grant any wish
a heart may desire.
He also told us that anyone
seeking a Dragon Ball
must pass tests of
bravery and intelligence
before an elder
will turn it over.
I offered to take
these tests, of course,
but he refused to give me
the Dragon Ball at any cost.
So I had no choice but to
take it... along with his life.
You cold-blooded
murderer!
[FRIEZA] At any rate,
after our difficulties
with the
first elder,
we found the next three
to be quite agreeable.
By the time we arrived,
they were all too willing
to hand over
their Dragon Balls.
Good, Frieza.
But after I beat you
to the next Dragon Ball,
you won't deal
with me so easily.
They did not
hand them over.
Our brothers would never
willingly give a Dragon Ball
to the likes of you.
Not in a million years!
Don't be so sure.
You underestimate our
powers of persuasion.
Zarbon, why don't
you show them?
Gladly.
[BOTH gasp]
Huuh...?!
[NAMEKS gasp]
Raagh!
No!
Raah!
[HENCHMAN 2 screaming]
[ELDERS gasp]
[ZARBON quietly grunting]
[ZARBON] Hyaaah!
[ELDER screaming]
[wimpering]
[ZARBON chuckles]
[ZARBON] Hmph.
[KRILLIN] Oh, man!
They killed him!
No...
[GOHAN growling]
[KRILLIN] Gohan, you gotta keep
your power level down.
They'll notice.
I'm just too angry.
I know it's hard.
But there was nothing either
of us could have done.
We can't beat these guys
fighting them head-on.
We're gonna
have to be smart
if we want to get
the Dragon Balls
and wish Piccolo and
the others back to life.
[GOHAN growling]
Whatever happens down
there, we just have to wait.
[KRILLIN growls]
What do you say?
Do you think you're ready to
start cooperating with us yet?
[FRIEZA cackles]
[DODORIA laughing]
[HENCHMEN laughing]
What do you want with
the Dragon Balls anyway?
Oh, just a
tiny little wish.
For the one thing I
don't already have:
The power of
eternal life.
Eternal life?
Well, that figures.
It's the same thing
Vegeta wants to wish for.
So I guess they really
are Vegeta's competition!
And they're winning.
Do whatever you
will with me,
but I'm still not going to
give you a Dragon Ball!
Of course not... Please,
you stubborn Namek...
You think
you're so noble...
Even under
threat of pain,
you refuse to surrender
your precious Dragon Ball.
Well, we'll see
how noble you are
when your children
are at stake.
Ah! Please, no!
Please! I'll
tell you anything!
[DODORIA chuckles]
[GOHAN growling]
[DODORIA] Hm?
What?!
[KRILLIN] Quick!
Get down!
[DODORIA]
Lord Frieza,
I'm picking up that
power level again.
[DODORIA]
Up there.
It came from just
over that ridge.
I think someone's
been watching us.
[ZARBON] Hmm...
[ZARBON] You seem to
have the situation
well under control here,
Lord Frieza,
perhaps I should
go check it out.
Huh? Now it's coming
from over there!
[BOTH gasp]
[laughs]
[growling]
[laughing]
Ah, finally!
[ZARBON] Hmph.
Uh?! More Nameks.
Do you think
it'll help?
[ALL] Haah!
[FRIEZA] Quite the
impressive landing.
It's too bad you
got here late.
Your friend could have
used your help earlier.
[gasps]
You! Who are you, and what
have you done to the elders?!
Who am I? I suppose
you could say,
I'm an aspiring
Dragon Ball collector.
And as for what I've
done to your elders...
Heh...
I'd say
that's obvious.
[NAMEK] Then the
rumors are true.
We've heard talk of a villain
attacking our people,
stealing the Dragon
Balls! You coward!
How dare
you do this?!
How dare you come here
and harm our people?!
[NAMEKS growling]
Huh?
[DODORIA chuckles]
[HENCHMAN 3 chuckles]
Be careful,
brothers.
These cretins are much
stronger than they appear!
Get 'em!
Oh, so you actually
mean to fight us?
Well, you wouldn't be
the first fools to try.
Dodoria?
[DODORIA] Let's see
what they've got.
[DODORIA laughs]
Better watch
out boys!
These Nameks are packing
some serious heat!
Their power level's
at 1,000 each!
[HENCMEN laughing]
[DODORIA chuckling]
I don't know, guys.
Maybe we'd better run away!
[thinking] Now I
understand how they were able
to find our
villages so quickly,
like they knew where
we were all along.
They use that little device
they wear over their eyes.
It must locate sources
of energy and power!
[GOKU]
9,999!
10,000!
[GOKU grunting]
Aahh...
[GOKU'S stomach growling]
Food...
I need food...
I'm so hungry I could
eat this whole ship...
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU thinking] Somewhere,
out in that darkness,
Vegeta's waiting for me.
And who knows what else!
I have to be ready
for anything.
And I don't
have much time!
Right!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
[HENCHMAN 4] Aw, hell! You guys
are way outta your league!
Maybe I should round up
a couple old grannies
for you to
fight, huh?
[DODORIA and FRIEZA chuckling]
No, the Nameks are just
suppressing their power levels.
But these lunkheads don't
seem to notice at all.
Remember how Vegeta and Nappa
didn't get it at first either?
[ZARBON giggling]
Let's gooo!
[ALL] Yaaah!
[HENCHMEN continue yelling]
Raaugh!
[NAMEKS yelling]
[BOTH] Huh?!
Raah!
[blows landing]
Hraagh!
Rrgh!
[HENCHMAN screaming]
Raagh!
[HENCHMAN 3 screaming]
Haah!
[fighting sounds]
Are you certain that their
power level is just 1,000 each?
Rrraaah!
I just can't
explain it!
Somehow, their power
level's at 3,000 now!
Go! Go! Go!
Atta way!
These Nameks are
actually holding their own.
It doesn't make sense!
My scouter is
working perfectly.
They must've figured out a
way to mask their power.
They were deliberately
trying to trick us!
Let's go, Nameks!
Good job!
That's the
way to do it!
[thinking] Hmm... There are only
three of those devices left.
If I could only
manage to destroy them.
Listen carefully,
children...
You must move away
from me at once.
[NAMEKIAN CHILDREN gasp]
Now, do as
I say! Go!
Dodoria.
Yeah?
[FRIEZA] It's time.
[DODORIA] Good.
I was getting
tired of waiting.
[DODORIA] So, do you
just want me to kill one
as an example?
[FRIEZA] Kill them all.
[ELDER NAMEK] Rrgh!
[DODORIA growling]
Is that it?
Stupid old Namek.
I've had worse
insect bites.
That's right!
Run away!
[ELDER NAMEK] Rrrgh...
What are
you doing?!
Rrgh!
[laughing]
The scouters!
I should have known.
That's what he's
aiming for!
[KRILLIN] That
crafty old dog.
[GOHAN] W-Wait a second.
Why is he just destroying
the scouters?
Think about it.
Without the scouters,
Frieza and his men won't be
able to find the Nameks
or the Dragon Balls!
Even if Frieza gets the Dragon
Ball he's looking for here,
he's gonna have a
heck of a time
tracking down
the next one.
You gotta admire him.
He's risking everything
to protect his people!
[DODORIA growling]
[DODORIA] You think you're
pretty smart, don't you?!
But you're not... Destroying
the scouters won't save you!
I'll have no mercy.
[GOHAN and KRILLIN growling]
[DODORIA]
Do you hear me?!
I'll kill all
you Nameks!
And I'm gonna
start with you!
Get out!
[DODORIA]
Ready to die?!
[NAMEKS gasping]
[NAMEKIAN CHILDREN whimpering]
Rraaugh!
[DODODRIA yelling]
[frightened gasping]
[NARRATOR] It seems the forces
of evil are about to claim
yet another victim.
Is there nothing Gohan
and Krillin can do
to save the Nameks from Frieza
and his powerful minions?
Only one thing
is certain...
The showdown with this
deadly foe continues,
next time on
Dragon Ball Z!