[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the match between Cell
and Gohan opened with a bang,
as Cell released a
merciless assault
on the 11 year-old powerhouse.
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR] And on-lookers
began to question if
Goku's confidence in
his son was well deserved
as the young boy
refused to fight back.
[PICCOLO] Goku, you fool!
We told you this
would happen. We told you!
But you just
wouldn't listen to us!
Not so fast, Piccolo!
Can't you sense
his energy? He's fine.
Huh?!
[NARRATOR] With an
explosive re-entrance,
Gohan showed that he'd
endured the android's attack
with only minor
scrapes and bruises.
Clearly, Gohan had the
potential to defeat Cell.
But the boy
did not want to fight,
afraid of what
his own powers would do.
[GOHAN] I've gotten
much stronger,
and if I were to lose control,
there's really no telling
how powerful I might become.
And there's no telling
what kind of damage
a power like that might cause.
Well, your story didn't work,
but you have given me
something to work for.
You see, Gohan...
this "hidden power"
of yours intrigues me,
and now that I know about it,
I'm determined
to see it for myself!
[GOHAN gasps]
[grunting]
[NARRATOR] Cell is
thirsty for a fight,
and his
curiosity is aroused.
Now that he knows
about Gohan's power,
Cell will not stop until
this hidden beast is uncaged.
[NARRATOR] Playing with Gohan
is like playing with dynamite.
But detonation is
exactly what Cell wants.
Just how far will he go?
What vicious
tactics will he employ
to light the Saiyan's fuse?
Well then. It looks like I might
actually get through to you yet!
[thinking] You can do this,
Gohan, I know you can.
Show everyone what an
incredible fighter you are!
What's happening down
there, Hercule?! Is it bad?
Of course it's bad! This is
no place for a child to be!
Unless a hero is found to
put down this terrible monster,
everyone on the
Earth will be massacred!
Must we all put our futures
in the hands of one fragile,
helpless little boy?
This reporter hopes not!
Mr. Satan, how's your stomach?
Ohh...
[MR. SATAN groans]
[MR. SATAN] Why'd you
make me think about it?!
--Oh, the pain!
--Well, there you have it,
the champ is still crippled
by a most lethal stomach virus!
We must be cursed for this
to happen to our greatest guy!
Gohan! Let's see if we can
give your engine a jump start!
Uh?
[GOHAN gasps]
Careful, Gohan! That's one of
Frieza's finishing moves!
Yeah! Step it up!
[GOHAN gasps,
CELL yells]
[CELL laughs]
[GOHAN screams]
[laughing continues]
[screaming continues]
Think about it!
A wretched way to die!
And no one can stop me!
[CELL chuckles]
[GOHAN screams]
[CELL] Except for you,
Gohan! Except for you!
Goku! Stop him!
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[GOHAN screams]
Come on!
I know this hurts you.
[GOHAN grunts]
What are you waiting for?!
I can feel your bones
beginning to crack,
so if you're going
to act, I'd do it now.
[GOHAN screams]
Ooh, the boy is being
squeezed like a ketchup bottle!
It's so horrible!
And I'm sure
if we don't get help,
Cell will torture
us all like this!
Oh, a tradic fate indead!
[PICCOLO growls]
No, I can't take it!
Goku, you can keep
standing there all you want,
but I'm helping Gohan!
No, you're not!
You and I both know you're
not strong enough to fight Cell!
So wait. Just
a little bit longer!
For what?
For Gohan to get killed?!
For Cell to rip him
to pieces while we watch?!
Wait until he has no choice.
[PICCOLO] Huh?
And then...
Right when Gohan is backed
into a corner with no way out,
he'll awaken his
furious inner strength.
[KRILLIN] Huh?
And when that happens,
you watch.
Gohan will break Cell
down once and for all!
[thinking] Has Kakarot
gone insane?!
How can he put so much
faith in the boy?!
[GOHAN screams]
That's it! Scream out!
Get angry! It makes you
mad that you're in pain!
[PICCOLO] Enough
of this game, Goku!
You're wrong about your son!
Gohan may have that power,
but it doesn't matter!
He doesn't thirst
for battle and mayhem!
He's not a fighter like you!
Huh?!
Do you want to know
what he's thinking?!
He's not thinking about
strength, or about competition!
He's wondering why his father is
standing there letting him die!
And so your son may be
the most powerful person
in the world, but he's also
a scared 11 year-old boy!
I'd rather die than wait!
[GOHAN screams]
[CELL growls]
[screaming continues]
[GOKU growls]
Krillin! Throw me a Senzu Bean!
Oh, sure!
[GOHAN groans]
[CELL chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOHAN wheezes]
Stubborn creature.
You refuse to fight back
despite all the pain
that I inflict on you.
Perhaps you'd
respond better
to the pain of your
dear, old friends?
[GOHAN gasps] Don't!
Ooh, Cell's taken flight!
[PICCOLO growls]
[CELL chuckles]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[gasping]
These are those nifty
Senzu Beans, right?
Well, you won't mind
if I hold on to them?
I was too late!
Darn Cell!
With these out of the way
I won't even have
to fight them myself.
[CELL chuckles]
Wait, what are you
planning to do?!
I'm going to do whatever
it takes to make you angry,
and bring out your full power!
And if your friends
end up dead,
then you can just blame
yourself for being so stubborn!
Please, don't do this!
If you unleash my power,
I won't be able to stop it!
I'll kill you!
[CELL laughs]
Oh, Gohan, I assure you
that once I've had my fill,
I'll stop you myself!
[PICCOLO] This is it!
Cell's about to make his move!
[GOKU groans]
I should've eaten a bean
when I had the chance!
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[CELL chuckles]
[GOHAN yells]
[BOTH grunt]
[GOHAN grunting]
That's the spirit.
Let your fury overcome you!
Huh?!
[ANDROID 16 growls]
16, stop this!
[growling continues]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER] What's this? Another
contestant has entered the fray!
Could this big, strange man
be the hero we've all
been waiting for?!
He got him!
Cell couldn't
detect his approach
because he's an android!
16's gonna try to
beat Cell on his own!
But why would he when
he knows it's just suicide?!
We've got to help him!
No, stay back, please!
Huh?
--Huh?
I will kill him
by self-destructing.
[CELL gasps]
[VEGETA gasps]
[TIEN gasps]
[YAMCHA gasps]
[TRUNKS growls]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[PICCOLO gasps]
Self destruct?!
I have a powerful explosive
embedded deep in my body.
It was intended
to be a last resort.
I am sorry that we Androids
have caused so much
suffering here on the Earth.
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL screaming]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Cell, no matter how
strong you have become,
you will not survive
this explosion!
[CELL grunting]
Cell, you destroy life.
You are a parasite
to this planet.
And I see now that this
is the best way to destroy you.
Doctor Gero's sick ambition
to terrorize the world
through us will
ultimately be put to rest
by his own devices.
[CELL grunts]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
Wow, he's really doing it!
[BOTH gasping]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Wait, uhhh...
I...
[ANDROID 16 yells]
[BOTH yelling]
[grunting]
[screaming]
Hey guys, you protect me!
[grunting, yelling]
I'm your master! You have to!
Ooh, Mommy!
Uh?
[ANNOUNCER] Huh...?
[ALL] Oh...?
So, where's the bang?
[KRILLIN growls]
WHAT?!
[CELL gasps]
Something is wrong!
The trigger's gone!
You can't, 16!
'Cause your bomb... was removed!
[ANDROID 16 gasps]
[gasping]
I, uh, overheard
Bulma talking about it.
You see, she...
She and her dad kinda
found that bomb of yours
while they were trying to
fix you and they removed it.
[ANDROID 16 screams]
My word, Bulma! Is that true?!
[BULMA] Mm-hmm...
We were worried...
[keyboard clacking]
[DR. BRIEF] Hmmm, that's odd.
Bulma, could you run
a second-level diagnostic
on his left chest plate?
One sec.
[keyboard clacking]
[DR. BRIEF] Oooh.
[DR. BRIEF] Well, that thing
could really lower the boom.
Take a look at those
neutron readings!
It's built like
a nuclear warhead!
You're right.
It appears Dr. Gero
designed this android
for a suicide mission.
I guess that was
intended for Goku.
There's always the possibility
that it still is. It's risky.
Let's take it out.
And so...
We got rid of it because
we just didn't trust him.
It's gone now! You'll have
to fight him another way!
[ANDROID 16 groans]
[CELL laughs]
Sorry, 16, I'm staying.
But if you have a deathwish, far
be it for me to let you down!
[CELL chuckles]
--[ANDROID 16 grunts]
--[CELL grunts]
[ANDROID 16 screams]
[gasping]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[BULMA screams]
He didn't?!
[GOKU growls]
[GOHAN gasps]
16. His petty existence
proved Dr. Gero had his flaws.
[GOHAN screams]
[ALL] Hmm...?
[screaming]
Oh my, Hercule! We're in public!
[MR. SATAN screams]
[PIIZA giggles]
You haven't done
that in a while!
Caroni, move that
thing away from us.
[MR. SATAN growls]
Yes sir!
[CARONI sighs]
[CARONI] Oh my...
[CARONI whines]
[screaming]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Does anyone else
want to be a martyr today?
[BOTH growl]
[VEGETA growls]
That scoundrel!
[GOHAN growls]
[CELL] So, Gohan, we still
haven't gotten you mad!
Let's try some
friendly persuasion.
[CELL] Let's see,
what do we have here?
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven.
That's easy enough.
[CELL yells]
[CELL growling]
What in the world is he
doing to his body now?
[growling continues]
[GOHAN gasps]
[CELL grunting]
[VEGETA gasps]
[CELL grunts]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[laughter]
What in the
heck are those things?
Somehow, Cell has
spit from his back...
One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven.
Seven monsters!
They look just like Cell,
except they're little and blue,
and, I don't know
what's going on!
[CROWD murmuring]
[laughter]
Now, my dear children.
Those seven on the
cliff are your enemies.
Give them pain.
Kill them,
if it makes you happy!
--[CELL chuckles]
--[GOHAN gasps]
Hop to it!
Guys! Be on guard;
they're all incredibly strong!
[PICCOLO growls]
[VEGETA growls]
Come on!
{VEGETA yells]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[CELL laughs]
Just try!
They may be small, but
they've inherited my powers!
[GOKU growls]
[laughter]
[BOTH growl]
[laughing continues]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[BOTH whimper]
[laughing continues]
[VEGETA growls]
[NARRATOR] Do the powers
of Cell have no end?
Anxious to unleash
Gohan's hidden strength,
Cell has let loose
a small army
of miniature androids
on the Z Fighters.
But what sort of powers
do these creatures possess?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball Z!