[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z,
two unwelcome guests, Frieza
and his father, King Cold,
descended upon the Earth,
only to be confronted by
a mysterious stranger,
a young man determined to thwart
their evil plans
single-handedly.
[NARRATOR] And when the
strange young man vanquished
Frieza's entire crew in a flash,
his bold purpose seemed
a little more plausible.
You're about to find out
what it's like to fight
a real Super Saiyan!
And I'm not talking about Goku!
What?!
[yelling]
No!
[NARRATOR] And so the battle
between the unknown
Super Saiyan and Frieza,
the Warlord of Evil, began!
[NARRATOR] After a blazing
attack at point blank range,
Frieza's father, the
wicked giant, King Cold,
was convinced that the
battle was already over.
When in fact, it had just begun.
Hey! Frieza!
Huh?!
[NARRATOR] Who is this
radical Super Saiyan?
And where did he come from?
FInd out today!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[grunting]
[KING COLD] Frieza!
[KING COLD wails]
They're right there! Look guys!
Huh?
[shouting]
[ALL gasping]
[KING COLD growls]
He... beat Frieza!
Effortlessly!
But who is he?
Who knows?!
Let's just hope this
guy's on our side!
[BULMA] You guys are crazy!
They just look like tiny
little dots way up there!
How can you even
tell who they are?
It's probably Goku, you guys.
Mister Super Saiyan.
He has a knack for showing
up at just the right time...
Yeah! He's such a stud! Gosh!
No, it's not Goku. No way.
--Huh?
But he's definitely
a Super Saiyan!
[VEGETA growls]
Wha--?!
See ya!
Wait up!
Man! Can't miss this!
Hold it, buddy-boy! I'm not
being left behind again!
Oh, wow!
[BULMA laughs]
This is great!
[YAMCHA] Hold still!
[KING COLD growls]
Super Saiyan.
I'm impressed.
To encounter a fighter
of your caliber
is a rare occurrence indeed.
But it does present
quite an opportunity.
You see, I can appreciate
a great talent such as yours.
My eyes are not blinded
by pride like my son's were.
Join me, and take Frieza's
place at my side
as the supreme ruler
of the universe!
Not a chance!
Now don't be too hasty...
Imagine:
This and every other world would
be but the merest of baubles
in your collection.
Play things for your amusement.
Subject to your every whim.
No?
Alright. But grant me this.
Allow me to examine your sword.
A weapon of such obvious quality
practically begs to be admired.
[KING COLD chuckles]
[KING COLD] You have
nothing to fear from me.
Hmm?
[BOY] So you want
to see my sword, huh?
Here! Catch!
[KING COLD chuckles]
[KING COLD] Yes...
Yes, indeed.
Remarkable craftsmanship.
And I have a hunch that you
would not have defeated my son,
were it not for this sword.
What do you say?
Believe what you want to.
Hah!
[KING COLD chuckles]
Alright then, I will!
[KING COLD] I say that without
this sword you're nothing!
That's what I believe!
[KING COLD growls]
[KING COLD yells]
[KING COLD gasps]
[KING COLD whimpers]
Heh.
[BOY] So much for your theory.
[KING COLD grunts]
[KING COLD yells]
You should know that a
weapon doesn't make the man!
Wait, you dirty, little Saiyan!
[KING COLD screams]
Huh?!
[gasping]
[KING COLD screams]
[KING COLD grunts]
First Frieza! Now him!
Whoa! Man!
[thinking] Who is this kid?
Wait! You can't! Nooo!
Please! I am
defenseless! Please?
I'm not bad! My son
was evil, but not I!
I wanted nothing but peace!
I meant you no harm!
I swear it!
I am-- I-It's the truth! Noo!
[ALL gasp]
Wow! Just like that!
Bam! They're gone!
[TIEN gasps]
And it looks to me like this guy
hasn't even come anywhere close
to breaking a sweat!
[KRILLIN] Yeah!
Let's just hope he doesn't
decide to come after us!
Hmm...?
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN whimper]
I'm heading off to a place
near here to meet Goku.
Would you guys like to come?
--What?
--Huh?
Wha...? How weird!
How does he know
about my father?!
[BOY] Come on, it's this way!
Goku should be arriving
there in a couple of hours!
[GOHAN] What...?
[ALL] Huh?
[thinking] Hmm. Alright.
What's this guy up to?
[thinking] I don't know who
he is, but he's no Super Saiyan!
Of that I'm certain! Kakarot
and I are the only Saiyans left!
He can't be one of us!
It's impossible!
Hey, follow me! Don't
worry, I won't bite! This way!
Well, I'm going for it!
He knows my Dad!
Yeah, possibly! But how?
We've known Goku his whole life.
I'm in! He seems
pretty cool to me.
Plus he saved us from Frieza.
He can't be all that bad, huh?
I say we go.
Well, I don't trust
that guy. No way.
You don't trust
me either. I say go.
Definitely! I've got
to find out who he is.
Huh?!
You're all nuts!
--[BULMA] Whoooo!
--[YAMCHA] Stop fidgeting!
[BOY] Wow! My tracking
unit still works
with the original satellite!
You rule, Gramps!
Yeah, this is it.
Look out, you guys!
He's up to something!
How about a cold drink?
Goku's not due to arrive
for two more hours.
It's pretty hot
and dry out here.
Well, I don't see why not.
Huh?
Yeah!
Wait! Gohan!
[BULMA] Chill out, Krillin!
They're just sodas.
[GOHAN] Ooh, wow!
What a great selection!
[BULMA] Hey! I'm starting to
like this guy! He has root beer!
[GOHAN] Orange for me!
Ahh! Good stuff!
Yeah! Super!
Is there a grape, guys?
[GOHAN] Ha, ha!
Yeah! Two grapes!
Oh boy!
Yeah!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laugh]
[BULMA] Have we met?
You look so familiar!
Uh, no. Sorry...
Excuse me, mister! But
how do you know my Dad?
Actually, I haven't
met your dad before.
I've only just heard about him.
[KRILLIN] Then how do you
know that he's going to arrive
at this spot
in two hours?
Well, that's uh...
Sorry, I... I can't say.
Why not? I'll tell you!
Because you're up to something!
Tell us now, tough guy!
Who are you?
I wish I could. Sorry...
[GOHAN] When you defeated
Frieza and that big guy,
you were a Super Saiyan,
weren't you?
Yes... yes I was.
That's a lie!
--Huh?
[VEGETA] Look my friend,
Kakarot, the one you call Goku,
and myself, are the
only Saiyans left!
Kakarot's kid there is half
Saiyan, so if you count him,
that makes three of us!
There's no way that you
could have Saiyan blood!
Huh?
Uh?
[GOHAN] Yeah, but.. we saw him!
He just defeated Frieza!
And that huge guy!
All by himself!
Well, I'm calling him
a liar! Not a weakling!
Huh?
Oh, hey! You've got our
logo on your jacket.
That's my Dad's company!
Are you one of our employees?
No! Not exactly. Just a fan.
Oh, I see! Well,
tell me your name,
and I'll recommend you to Dad!
I, uh, can't do that...
I'm sorry, I know it's strange.
Ooh! Mystery man!
Is his shoe size a secret too?
Yeah! Why can't I
have a secret name?
That's not fair! I bet you have
a secret spy decoder ring too!
Knock it off, you guys!
You're all jealous!
This guy just beat Frieza
single handedly! So there!
Right!
Hah.
[OX-KING] Hey, Hello!
[OX-KING gasps]
Hey, ChiChi!
What is all that junk?
It's the latest
in study equipment.
It teaches kids while
they're sleeping.
[OX-KING] What?
Since I can't get Gohan
to study during the day,
I'll just cram it
into his brain at night!
Oh, yes! He'll be tired
when he gets home.
So we'll start him off
with a little math.
What makes him think he
can just fly off like that
without saying a word?!
It's that TV!
--I'm throwing the TV away!
--ChiChi! No!
[VEGETA] What are
you looking at?!
[BOY] Oh, uh, nothing. It's just
that I, uh, like your shirt.
[VEGETA] You would.
[GOHAN] Hey,
Piccolo, do you mind
if I ask you about something?
What's that?
Well, uh... When Dende
and the other Nameks
left to resettle
on that new planet
you could've gone with them.
I was wondering why you
chose to stay here with us?
They're your people.
Well, I might join them
some day. But for now,
I feel like my mission
is here on Earth.
Sometimes connections
between people run deeper
than where they're from or
what color skin they have.
Hey! Now check this out!
Is it me? Or do those
two kind of look alike?
Well, now that you mention it,
I can kind of see a resemblance.
Well.. I mean just in looks.
That other guy
seems pretty nice.
But Vegeta has the
personality of a stump.
Well, he's a prince.
So what?
Princes have to act bored.
Like the world's not
good enough for them.
Huh? Vegeta seems more
agitated than bored.
Like he's got a bad case of
hemorrhoids or something.
[VEGETA] Why do you
keep looking over here?!
Haven't you ever seen
a pink shirt before?!
If you like it that much,
you can have it!
No, no thank you.
Then knock it off, kid!
Maybe Goku met
this guy somewhere
out in space, Chiaotzu.
He has been gone a while.
But he told Gohan that
he hasn't met Goku.
[TIEN] But how can
he know the exact spot
that Goku is going to land
two hours before he arrives?
[YAMCHA] Maybe he's wrong!
Maybe Goku's not coming!
[ALL] Huh?
[BULMA] Well, the
only way to find out
is to wait two hours, right?
--[YAMCHA] Yeah!
--[PUAR] Uh-huh!
[BULMA] Well, how
long has it been?
[YAMCHA] One hour.
[BULMA} Well, then, just
chill out for one more hour!
[YAMCHA] Well, you can
find another ride home!
[BULMA] Fine!
Oops! Uh, sorry!
[BOY] Hey, uh, that's it!
Two hours have passed!
Goku should be arriving
any second now!
--[KRILLIN] Huh?
--[BULMA] Really?
Okay...?
Huh...?
Huh?!
[CHIAOTZU] Oh, my gosh! Tien!
I know! I feel it too, Chiaotzu!
He's coming!
Man, that guy was
right after all!
You're all nuts!
My woman's intuition
isn't picking up anything
at all right now.
No, it's true!
He's finally home!
My Dad's back!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Look! Up there! Dad!
[BULMA] Wow! Cool!
[KRILLIN] Last one
there is a rotten egg!
[BULMA] Hey! Wait for me!
[BULMA} Wait up!
[GOHAN] Wow! Check it out!
What a crater!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, no kidding!
Boom! What a landing!
I hope he has some
air bags in that baby!
[YAMCHA] Why? To protect
the ship from Goku's head?
[TIEN] Yeah, really!
[gasping]
[GOHAN gasps]
Huh...? Hey, guys.
--[BULMA] Yeah! You made it!
--[cheering, whooping]
--What took you so long, Dad?!
[cheering, whooping]
--Goku!
--[cheering, whooping]
Welcome back to Earth, Goku!
How did you guys know
that I was coming?
[NARRATOR] At long last,
Goku is reunited with
his family and friends.
But how did this mysterious
stranger know the exact time
and place of his arrival?
Is he friend or foe?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball Z!