[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
no sooner had Vegito landed
in Majin Buu's stomach
than he was blown apart!
[GOKU, VEGETA gasp]
[NARRATOR] The one had
become two once again!
[NARRATOR]
And the search was on.
Goku and Vegeta were
looking for their sons
who, along with Piccolo,
had been absorbed
into the inner workings of Buu.
[NARRATOR] But this rescue
mission could only work
if the rescuers
managed to stay alive.
[NARRATOR] Into the deadly
gastric juices they plunged
until Vegeta created an ulcer
through which the duo
made a narrow escape!
[NARRATOR]
But one peril led to another
in this living house of horrors.
And the Saiyan
team was attacked
by millions of deadly
acid-bearing organisms!
[VEGETA, GOKU grunt]
[NARRATOR]
And when these little guys
bite off more than
they can chew,
they summon the big boss who
comes to finish off the job.
[VEGETA gasps]
What?
--Look out!
--[GOKU yells]
[VEGETA]
Son of a Namek! What is it?
[GOKU]
I don't know!
[FLAT HEAD roars]
[GOKU yells]
Kakarot! It's the slime!
The creature is communicating
with it! Get rid of it, quick!
[yells]
I can't!
[GOKU growls,
VEGETA gasps]
[FLAT HEAD roars]
[gasps]
Kakarot! Do something!
[FLAT HEAD roars]
[GOKU yells]
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
What's goning on?!
Phew!
And you were talking about me!
Why don't you just blow
a trumpet or something
and announce we're
here, Mr. Undercover!
Oops! Too much, huh?
I thought I was being subtle,
but I guess I did
get carried away!
[VEGETA growls]
--[distant growling]
--Huh?!
[VEGETA]
Oh, great! Now what?
[GOKU]
There's no tellin'!
[distant moaning]
[BOTH]
Hm?
[roaring]
[BOTH yell]
[ROUNDER]
You hurt my big brother!
[BOTH yell]
Oh, no! Flat Head!
What have they done?!
Daddy! Flat Head's hurt!
Wow! If they're that big,
just imagine how big
their father must be!
Disgusting!
No, I do not want to imagine
even one more slimy little--
[BOTH yell]
[FATHER WORM growls]
Wow! Now that's
what I call a worm!
[VEGETA retches] Kakarot,
I think I'm going to puke!
Dad! Those two guys
were picking on me!
Look! Let's blast him!
There's no sense
in tip-toeing around!
Buu knows that we're down here!
What? He does? Wow!
How do you know?
Hey! What if you're wrong?
Haaaa!
[sighs]
[FLAT HEAD]
I told you, Dad! They're mean!
[ROUNDER]
Beat them up, Daddy!
[BOTH gasp]
[WORMS laugh]
[FLAT HEAD]
Ow! What's the big idea, Dad?!
[FATHER WORM] No one
likes little smart alecks!
[WORMS gasp]
[FLAT HEAD]
But they hurt me, Dad!
They could have destroyed you!
How many times have I told
you never to leave the pack?!
[growls]
[FLAT HEAD whimpers]
I'm sorry, Dad!
[FATHER WORM] Please forgive
my son? He's young!
Sure, no problem.
[VEGETA growls]
Ah, that's just great!
Now he's making
friends with worms!
[FATHER WORM]
They both have a bad habit
of trying to eat
anything that moves!
You should think about teaching
those little ingrates of yours
some better manners!
That's what he's doing!
Hey! Maybe you
could lend us a hand.
We're trying to find our sons.
Did you happen to
see them anywhere?
[ROUNDER]
Ah! I've seen them!
[FLAT HEAD]
There was a green man, too!
[GOKU]
Huh...?
Piccolo, too!
[VEGETA whimpers]
Say! Do you know where
they are right now?
[SUPER BUU wails]
[whimpering]
Yes! Thank goodness!
[MR. SATAN]
Look what it is!
Wow! Out here? Luxury. I could
use one of those things myself!
An Evacuation Station?
Hey! It's time!
Time?! For what?!
What d'ya think?! What we got
here is a golden opportunity!
[DENDE]
Wait! Hey, it's occupied!
Huh...?
I'm not gonna go poop,
I'm gonna go in there and kick
his lilly-livered boohonkus!
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna-- Huh?!
[farting]
[DENDE]
Good heavens!
[MR. SATAN]
He dropped the bomb!
[BOTH whimper]
[BEE whimpers,
MR. SATAN groans]
[FLAT HEAD] The green guy
went off that way!
[ROUNDER] Yeah! That's where
the other one's went, too!
[BOTH]
Hm?
[VEGETA]
Well, that looks inviting.
What's going on?!
[GOKU gasps]
[WORMS yelling]
[FLAT HEAD]
Dad! What's going on?!
[FATHER WORM]
Looks like it's potty time!
[GOKU] Hey, you guys!
What the heck is "party time"?
Where is this taking us?!
[WORMS yell]
[GOKU]
Man! Some party!
[VEGETA] They said "potty time",
not "party time"!
Looks like we're not gonna make
the most graceful of exits!
Not me!
What do you propose we do?
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA]
Run!
Wait up! Hey!
[GOKU]
Are you crazy?!
[toilet flushes]
[SUPER BUU sighs]
I'm glad that's over!
Those guys were
a pain in the rear.
Who would have thought
that this insolent world
could have strong
guys like that?
[SUPER BUU] Who's the most
powerful being in the Universe?!
Me! Majin Buu! That's who!
[laughs]
[laughing continues]
[GOKU] So this is what it's like
inside Majin Buu's head!
Gohan and the others
have to be in here
because this is the
only place we haven't looked.
[VEGETA]
Hm?
[VEGETA] Okay, use your
instincts, Kakarot.
Right or left?
[GOKU]
Hmm... I'd have to say... Left!
Good! Then I'm going right.
[GOKU yelps]
[GOKU]
That's not very nice!
You follow your instincts
and I will follow mine.
Fine! Have it your way.
[GOKU]
Hmph!
I'm glad I'm not united
with him any more! Sheesh!
[GOKU]
What a strange place.
[gasps]
Who are you?
Come into the light!
Gohan!
[VEGETA]
Hm?!
Excellent! Nice work, boys.
You're alive and well.
Good! Let's go find
Kakarot. Follow me.
[VEGETA] The sooner we get
out of here, the better!
[BOTH]
Fuu-sion! Haa!
[VEGETA]
Huh?!
What is this?
[KIBITO KAI]
It's Gohan! And Gotenks!
Superb! They succeeded!
Yes! Now they can escape.
But why would the boys
do a Fusion technique
unless they were preparing
themselves for a big fight. Hmm?
[KIBITO KAI]
I see.
All right! Let's get out of
this place. Whatd'ya say, son?
Gohan! What's the big idea,
son? Why did you do that?!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA squeals]
All right!
You're asking for it, kid!
Look here, whatever you are!
[VEGETA yells]
Where are our sons?!
[VEGETA grunts]
Fool! You know you're just
digging your own grave!
Why? And how?!
Gohan's too pure to be taken
over by the forces of darkness!
Calm your mind and look!
Things are not
as they appear, Kai.
They're in an arena where
Buu's thoughts can take form.
Gohan and the others are
thought-forms created by Buu.
How do you beat a thought, Sir?
[OLD KAI]
Good question!
[GOKU] I can tell by
the look in your eyes
that you're not my son!
[GOKU grunts]
You're not my son,
but you punch like him.
So be it, you fake!
[yells]
[growls]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[BEE yelps]
Where is he? That toxic gas
can't finish me!
Huh?!
[yells]
[stomach growling]
I'd better get a bite
No sense destroying the
world on an empty stomach.
Ha, ha, ha! Look at him go!
Taking off like a bird
trying to escape from
the mighty Mr. Satan!
[laughs]
Stop wasting time.
Let's track him down.
Say what?! I thought you knew!
Look! I don't want to fight him!
Well, that's good, because
no sane person would!
But we're gonna do it anyway!
T-T-T-Tell me-me h-how?
Well, he said that he was gonna
get something to eat, right?
Well, I'm sure he'll let his
guard down while he's eating.
Then, we got him!
[thinking]
Oh, boy!
Maybe I can do it!
Hiyaaa! Take that! Uhh...
Maybe... Maybe
I've lost my marbles!
Fighting Buu, well,
that would be suicide!
I need to ditch the kid
and hide somewhere!
[DENDE]
Let's go!
Wait! Why so soon? Let's stay
here and make a plan! Ahhh!
Heeeyyyyy!
[VEGETA growls, grunts]
[grunts]
[GOTENKS grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
Fighting both of those idiots
at once is pretty tough!
Where is that silly
clown when you need him?
Special Beam Cannon!
[GOTENKS screams,
PICCOLO grunts]
Now that was a close call!
Huh?!
[VEGETA] Those were direct hits!
Y-You were both out cold!
Shoot! What are they?!
[GOKU]
Ka... me...
[BOTH]
...ha... me... haaa!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA]
Now what?
[GOKU]
Huh? Hey!
You did that?!
[GOKU]
It was an accident! Huh?
[gasps]
[VEGETA] I don't think these
ghoulish imposters
can be destroyed.
They just keep getting up!
[GOKU]
I've noticed!
[VEGETA]
So, uh, any ideas?
[GOKU]
Not right off hand!
I smell cake!
[thinking]
There he goes.
[chuckles]
[SUPER BUU]
It's cake time!
[GOTENKS chuckles]
Not even a little scratch!
These look-a-likes are
not made of flesh and bone!
Yeah! But it sure
does feel like it
when these guys come after us!
Ka-me-ha-me...
[GOTENKS GHOULS laugh]
Man! We're in big trouble!
[SUPER BUU]
Oooh!
Aaah!
Lemon pound cake!
And strawberry shortcake!
And German chocolate!
[laughs]
Oh yeah! Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah! Ha, ha!
[GOKU]
He's cake!
[screams]
[VEGETA]
Toast, Kakarot! He's toast!
[GOKU]
No! He's really cake!
Yes! I see! Chocolate!
[GOKU]
No! Strawberry!
[VEGETA]
Cupcakes?!
[GOKU]
No! Pound cake!
What? I-I-I-I-Is
this good?! Or bad?!
Neither! This is incredible!
That buffoon Majin Buu just
couldn't keep his
thoughts straight!
All he can think
about are pastries!
[OLD KAI laughs]
[MR. SATAN] Oh, I'm getting
a bad feeling about this!
[DENDE]
Shhh!
[DENDE gasps]
[MR. SATAN]
Did he see us?
[DENDE]
I don't think so!
[VEGETA]
He's got cobwebs in his head!
But that's about
all that's up here!
Where could they have gone?
[VEGETA]
Kakarot! Heads up!
Uh?
Over here! Take a look!
Hey!
Well, check him!
See if he's alive
before you celebrate!
He is! Wonderful!
Hey! Over there,
Vegeta! There's more!
Gohan! And Goten! And Trunks!
We did it! We did it!
We found them!
[GOKU laughs]
[VEGETA]
Are they all right?
[GOKU] Yeah! They're doing fine!
Considering where they are!
[NARRATOR]
Majin Buu continues to gorge
with our heroes in his head.
Will Goku and Vegeta be able
to free the others and escape?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!