[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan summoned all
of his strength
to remove the legendary Z Sword
from its sacred resting place.
[GOHAN grunts]
[NARRATOR] If what Kibito and
the Supreme Kai say is true,
this mythical weapon
may give Gohan
the power he needs
to defeat Majin Buu.
Meanwhile, the
pudgy pink monster
prepared himself a feast
of unsuspecting victims.
[BUU]
Chocolate!
[NARRATOR] In an instant,
another city's population
was transformed into
thousands of tasty treats.
And this is still
only the beginning.
Buu will have
to devour far more
before his hunger for
destruction is satisfied.
The entire globe is in
danger of being gobbled up!
But all hope is not lost.
[GOKU] So the two of you should
start practicing fusion.
[NARRATOR] Goten and
Trunks are ready to
begin learning the
fusion technique,
and with Gohan in
training worlds away,
a hero may soon emerge
to defeat Majin Buu!
[GOKU] The fusion technique
is kind of like a dance.
You have to perform a
specific series of movements,
and your timing
has to be right on.
It's not that
difficult to learn, but...
It does take a lot of practice.
So, if you're ready,
we'll begin.
[GOKU]
C'mon, guys, what's wrong?
You know,
I don't think this fusion
stuff's as great as you say.
Why don't you just
give it a shot?
Okay, but it sounds kinda
stupid if you ask me.
I mean, it's not like
we're gonna beat Majin Buu
by dancing on him.
[GOKU]
That's enough, Trunks.
Now, both of you,
go Super Saiyan.
Fine. Whatever.
[GOKU] Okay, now we're
getting somewhere.
Next step: raise your levels
as high as they can go.
Well, he asked for it, right?
Yeah. [chuckle]
[BOTH yell]
What is that?
[VIDEL]
What's going on, you guys?
Don't worry. That's just Goten
powering up. Trunks, too.
Not surprising. He does
take after his father.
[MR. POPO] Ahh. There's a
sound I recognize.
It's comforting in
a way, isn't it?
It makes me think those
boys can really do this.
Yes.
Amazing and at their age...
Good, now raise
it to your maximums.
[BOTH]
Huh...? We did.
[GOKU]
Oh. Well, in that case,
Trunks, your level's
a little too high.
Heh, heh.
If you want the fusion to work,
both of your power levels
must be exactly the same.
[GOKU] Trunks, take yours
down a bit to match Goten's.
[TRUNKS]
Right, take it down a bit.
So, something like this?
[GOKU] No. That's too low.
A little bit more...
More...
More!
There! That's perfect!
Remember how that feels.
That's exactly where
you guys want to be.
Great. Now back to normal.
Phew!
That's pretty tough, but why
do I have to do all the work?
Why can't Goten raise
his level to match mine?
I'm sorry, I couldn't.
It's okay, Son.
Trunks is older than you.
So it's only natural that he's
a little bit stronger, too.
[BULMA]
Excuse me, Goku.
But I don't want you
doing anything in here
that's going to hurt my son!
Bulma no, wait!
[BULMA]
Let me through!
You can't disturb
their training.
I certainly can!
Uh... You can't go!
[BULMA]
I am going!
[KRILLIN]
You can't!
[BULMA]
I am!
[KRILLIN]
Sorry about this, Bulma!
Aww, mom...
Krillin, you put me down!
I have every right to
be in here! Let go of me now!
I'm only following orders.
You guys are just too pig-headed
to think that your training
could benefit
from a woman's touch.
[GOTEN] I-I want to try it
again. How about you, Trunks?
[TRUNKS]
I'm ready!
Heh. Those kids.
Reminds me of me and Goku.
[KRILLIN grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
Wow, Krillin!
You're just too strong!
Bring it down to match Goku.
Phew...
[laughs]
Goku, I bet you wish
you could be like me.
Ah! Those were the days!
[MR. SATAN] You asked for it
and you got it, people!
The only man left on this planet
who can save you now is me!
I will save the
trees, the oceans.
I'll save the mountains,
the women, and the children.
I'll even save the bugs
from that evil Majin Buu!
You can count on me!
Get that monster, Champ!
Save our city!
But right now, my loyal fans,
I must continue
my rigorous training.
I will endure
hardships of the likes
of which you will
never see in your lives.
And until my training is over,
I shall bid you farewell!
[CROWD cheers]
[chuckles]
[thinking] This is a frightening
time for these people.
It's good to give
them some hope.
But what am I gonna do when
Majin Buu actually shows up?
Uhh...
Probably best not to think
too much about that.
I'll just keep trying to fly.
I mean, it might help
out my fighting some, yeah.
Oh yeah!
[CROWD chanting] Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
[screaming]
[BABIDI laughs]
[BUU giggles]
[squeals]
[grunting]
[BUU laughs]
[DRIVER yells]
[BUU]
Boing! Boing! Boing! Boing!
--Boing! Boing! Boing!
--[DRIVER yelling]
[BUU giggles]
[DRIVER screams]
[giggles]
[REPORTER] In their attempts to
find the elusive Majunior,
Goten, and Trunks,
the evil Majin Buu,
along with the wizard Babidi
continue to devastate the world!
When ever will this madness end?
Ooh, what an oogey mess!
I wish someone would just
turn those three cowards in!
Oh, could it be?
Get him, Trunks! You make that
boy sorry he ever met you!
[CROWD gasps]
My goodness people all
across the world are dying
and it's because that little
hooligan won't show his face!
If I knew where he was
I'd tell Babidi myself.
I know, Mom. He lives at
Capsule Corp in West City.
You sure about that?
Then we should all three
concentrate. You hear me, Ikose?
We should try to reach
Babidi with our minds! Now.
[giggles]
Now where should we go next?
[IDASA'S MOM] Babidi? Babidi?
Can you hear me?
[BABIDI]
What's that?
I think you should
know that Trunks
lives at the Capsule
Corporation in West City.
Now you can go there
and give that little hoo-hah
what he has coming to him!
Who is this?
Why I'm the head of the
PTA at my son's school,
so it's my duty
to do what I can
to end this whole
silly situation.
Besides, that dirty little
Trunks cheated at the tournament
today and stole the
title from my son Idasa!
Of course, my boy was feeling
a little under the weather
or I'm sure he would have
pounded that stupid little boy
into mincemeat!
I've told him that's no excuse
I'm raising champions,
not losers, you know!
That's not
important, really.
What is important is that you
go and teach him a lesson!
And I tell you right no--
Shut up!
And thank you for sending me
this wonderful information.
But if I hear your annoying
screech of a voice again.
I will kill you!
[shrieks]
I try to do one nice thing
and this is how I'm treated?!
[growls]
This time, I want you to
power up as much as you can
without actually
going Super Saiyan.
It'll be easier to
concentrate on learning
if you're not under
so much physical strain.
[BABIDI using ESP] Attention,
Earthlings! Attention!
So sorry to bother
you once again,
but I've recently
acquired some information
I couldn't wait to pass along.
You know, Trunks,
I am very eager to meet you.
And if I can't
get you to come to me,
then I'll just have to
come to where you live.
[BABIDI using ESP] It's a place
called Capsule Corporation
and it's located in West City.
I hope that you're
there to see me when I arrive,
because if you're not,
then your friends
and your family
will have to pay the price.
[growls]
Darn! Somebody-Somebody
told that creep where I live!
I can't let him get there!
My grandma and grandpa
are still at home!
Are you going?
I just heard everything!
My mother and father
are going to be killed!
Don't worry about it.
We can just bring them
back with the dragon balls.
And everyone else in the city?
What about them?!
We can bring everyone else back
to normal with the second wish.
[PICCOLO]
That's impossible.
Don't forget, we've already
used our first wish
to bring back everyone
from the tournament,
which leaves us one wish
to repair the rest of
Majin Buu's ruin.
Oh, yeah,
I guess you're right there.
[laughs]
[growls]
[GOKU]
Hmmm...
I've got an idea.
I'll bet you...
if we ask really nice
Shenron will let us wish
for two new wishes!
Would that work?
Sure, why not?
Well, I suppose it wouldn't
hurt anything to ask him.
Listen, if we let Majin Buu get
to the West City and destroy it
then he'll destroy
the Dragon Radar, Goku!
[gasps]
[GOKU] Yeah, that does
pose a problem.
Trunks, listen up.
I need you to go to Capsule Corp
and bring back the radar.
Huh?!
[GOKU] While you do that,
I'll get in front of
Babidi and Majin Buu
and try to slow them down.
Are you sure about that? Those
guys are pretty tough, you know.
They're going to
wanna fight back.
Yeah, but you let
me worry about them.
I'll be okay. Now, hurry up
before they get ahead of you.
[BULMA]
Trunks?
You gotta promise.
Please come back here
if things get too
dangerous for you.
[TRUNKS]
I promise.
You fly fast and
get back here safe.
You got it!
[GOKU]
Good luck, Trunks!
[thinking]
I wonder if I should even leave?
Nah, they'll be fine.
Right, time to fly!
Don't worry, Bulma.
Trunks is a resourceful
little guy. He'll be all right.
I know.
No, I mean it!
Vegeta isn't the
only one of his parents
he takes after, you know.
Thank you.
[GOKU]
Goten? I want you to stay here
and hold down
the fort for me, okay?
'Kay!
[GOKU]
Good.
You're a good boy.
That's it.
[BABIDI] No! Too fast!
I can't hold on! Slow down!
Help me! Please slow down!
[BABIDI screams]
[screams]
Would you quit playing
around like a child
and get me to West City?!
Okay!
[BUU]
Whoa!
[whimpers]
[BABIDI]
What happened? Why did you stop?
[gasps]
Hi.
[BABIDI]
You're alive...
I was certain you'd been
disposed of by Vegeta,
but it seems you're
still breathing.
Well good, I was afraid
I wouldn't get a chance
to thank you for helping me
bring Majin Buu back to life.
[whistles]
Vegeta and I both
underestimated your monster.
We didn't want to believe
the stories were true.
We never would've
let you succeed
if we knew he'd
be this powerful.
[laughs]
So, why did you come?
Did you come to tell us
how powerful we are?
Or... did you come
to join our efforts?
Maybe, maybe you came to tell me
where the other two brats are!
[GOKU]
Not in a million years, Babidi!
For your information,
one of those brats is my son.
I'm here to give you a warning.
A warning? You came to
warn us? Oh, that's funny!
[giggles]
Oh, I'm so scared!
Now this is something I think
the entire planet should hear.
[giggles]
[GOKU] I want you to
listen very carefully.
The three people you're looking
for will appear soon enough.
That, I promise.
So if I were you,
I wouldn't touch another
thing until they get here.
[BABIDI]
Why should we stop?
Are they planning
something special for us?
[GOKU] Yes, and when they've
finished they're training,
they'll destroy you.
[gasps]
[giggles]
[BABIDI, BUU laugh]
They can train all day,
they'll never be stronger
than the two of us!
[laughing continues]
Oh, you'll see.
[BABIDI, BUU laugh]
I don't think we'll
be waiting for that.
Tell them to show themselves
or we'll continue eliminating
all the people on this planet.
[giggles]
And tell them
that we'll start
with whoever we find at
this Capsule Corporation!
[giggles]
Oh well, guess
it was worth a shot.
You know, before you
get to Capsule Corp
your going to have
to go through me!
[BABIDI laughs]
[BABIDI] That's a good one!
Buu, you heard what he said!
Go through him!
I suppose he wants to end up
just like his friend Vegeta.
[giggles]
What's wrong?
[BUU giggles]
Huh...?
[burps]
[giggles]
You fool!
You're aiming that
stuff the wrong way!
Turn around and aim at him!
You! Show him what you're
made of! Hurry! Do it!
Okay, I do it.
--[BUU giggles]
--[BABIDI sighs]
[GOKU]
I don't get it.
You're a thousand times
stronger than Babidi.
Why do you let him boss
you around like this?
--[BUU] Huh...?
--[BABIDI gasps]
Don't listen! [growls]
And you'd better
keep your trap shut
if you know what's good for you!
[BABIDI growls]
[BABIDI] I resurrected Majin Buu
so he belongs to me!
Of course he's going
to do what I say!
[BUU growls]
Hey, do you want to
go back inside your ball
for another million years?!
Buu stuck back in ball,
you go bye-bye.
He gonna make you dead.
[thinking] That's the
problem with cronies.
No matter how dumb
they start off,
they all end up trying
to think for themselves.
No worry. Buu make you saved.
Me no like this
guy more than you.
Huh...? [sighs]
Well, so much for talk.
Buu have big fun now.
I'd like all the people of
the world to watch this.
A perfect example of
what will happen to anyone
who tries to stand in our way.
[giggles]
[GOKU growls]
Here we go!
[yells]
[gasps]
I can feel my dad's energy!
I know, your father
is an incredible man, Goten.
Whoa, unreal!
I can sense Goten's dad
from all the way over here!
He must be as strong
as... as my dad!
[laughs]
So, it's this trick again!
What a waste of energy!
Vegeta did the same thing and
look at what happened to him!
[BUU laughs
I'm guessing an
ascended Super Saiyan
isn't much of a
challenge for you.
So how about I take it
up to the next level?
The next level of a scented,
super something or, or
what? What's that?
Goku, what are you doing?
[NARRATOR]
Can Goku really push his powers
as far as he says he can?
And, if so, will he be able to
stall Majin Buu and Babidi
long enough for Trunks to
find the Dragon Radar?
Only one thing is certain,
if he can't, West City,
along with the rest of the
world will be doomed!
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!