[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
[GOKU]
Gohan!
[GOHAN]
Dad! Unbelievable!
Hi, Son! It's great
to hear your voice!
This is great! Father!
Are you really coming back?!
[NARRATOR]
That's right, Gohan!
Goku is allowed to
come back for a day!
And he's going to use
his leave to compete
in the World
Martial Arts Championship!
[KRILLIN] What?! No way!
Goku's gonna compete!
I don't believe it!
This is amazing! Wow!
Goku! Well, whatd'ya know...
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
it didn't seem likely
that Krillin could escape
from his family duties
to fight in the tournament.
But when the prize money
was mentioned,
Eighteen decided
that participating
in the World Championships
would be a family affair!
High above the Earth,
Gohan extended
another invitation
to a well known warrior.
Goku! If he's entering,
it should be one to remember!
[GOHAN]
So, whatd'ya say?!
[PICCOLO]
Sure! I'll do it!
[POPO] I'll bet Dende would
enjoy the tournament!
Hey, thanks!
But, I'm not much of a fighter!
[NARRATOR]
Lastly, Gohan broke the news
of Goku's return to
a certain small family
residing in the country!
Good news, son! You get
to meet your Daddy!
Isn't that wonderful?! Ohhh!
[NARRATOR] And so, Gohan,
choosing his younger brother,
Goten, as his training partner,
began his training
for the Tournament!
Alright! Nice warm-up!
Now! Let's get started!
[GOHAN] This is a little
trick Dad taught me!
Pretty cool, wouldn't you say?
Yeah!
[DENDE]
Amazing!
He's been in that state
for over 24 hours now!
[POPO] 27 hours, 9 minutes,
and 42 seconds to be exact!
[DENDE]
Wow!
[POPO]
Oh, no! Don't do it!
Oh, dear! Too late!
That makes 14 butterflies!
[DENDE]
Don't worry, Mr. Popo.
That's only one butterfly
every two hours!
Besides, I think this might
actually take care of
our mosquito problem
once and for all!
And watch-- I think I can help!
[POPO]
What do you mean, Dende?
[DENDE]
I don't think it's too late
for those last two casualties!
Just a little touch
should do it!
[POPO]
Oh, my goodness! You saved them!
Honey! Wait! Not yet!
What about my coffee!
What about my breakfast!
This isn't fair!
[EIGHTEEN] You're gonna
have to earn your breakfast!
[KRILLIN] I think you're
getting carried away!
Ahhh!
[ROSHI] Wow! Heh. Doesn't
she have him on his toes!
Heh!
[KRILLIN, EIGHTEEN grunting]
[MARON yawns]
[GOHAN]
Ahhhh! Now, that was good!
Well! Whatd'ya say,
sport? Shall we?
You bet!
[GOHAN] Thanks, Mom!
It was great! See ya!
[GOTEN]
Bye-bye, Mom!
Goten!
I don't want you to get
in your big brother's way
while he's training, understand?
[GOTEN]
Huh?
[CHICHI] This tournament
is very important!
We're expecting Gohan
to do really well
so he can win the prize money
and we can have
money to live on!
I want you to promise
not to interfere
with his training!
I promise, Mom!
I won't interfere!
You'd better not! I know you!
[GOHAN]
C'mon, Goten! Let's go!
We don't have all day, you know!
[GOTEN]
Gotta go, Mom! See ya!
Behave yourself! Bye!
[GOTEN laughs]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOTEN]
Ha, haaa!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
Goten! Where'd you go?
[GOHAN] I guess I went
too fast for the little guy!
[GOTEN laughing]
[GOHAN]
Hm? Hey, Goten! Where are you?
Over here!
I'm being attacked
by a wild dinosaur!
Please, help me!
Gohan, come over here
and meet my new friend!
He reminds me of Icarus! Hey!
[GOTEN laughing] Gohan!
Help me! It tickles! Please!
[GOHAN thinking]
Goten! So simple and happy!
Mom says that Dad was
like that when he was a boy!
Crazy little kid!
Hey! Goten!
I'm gonna get started!
I'll see you in a little bit!
What?! What's the matter
with you, Baba?!
Arranging such a thing
without my permission!
Are you crazy?
Look! Why not? Goku deserves it!
Don't be an old fuddy-duddy!
[GRAND KAI] How dare you,
you old dirty bag!
[KING KAI]
Now, now! Easy there, you two!
Look at how determined
and focused he is now!
Do you really have
the heart to tell him
that he can't go
back home and compete?!
Besides, Grand Kai!
You're the one he really
wants to train under!
If you want him to stay,
give him a lesson!
He's right! Goku's bored!
He needs a challenge.
Why don't you train him?!
What?! Uh, Goku? Train?
I-In his current condition,
I'm not sure his, uh, body
could withstand the
art of Grand Kai!
[GRAND KAI coughs]
Yes, perhaps this tournament
isn't such a bad idea after all,
if you know what I mean.
[BABA]
Hm!
Nyaaa!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOTEN]
Gohan!
Take a look at this!
[GOHAN] I hope it's
something important!
It is! Looky!
Oh... Wow, yeah...
[GOTEN] Gohan! Look at
the size of this guy!
He's huge! Ha, ha!
Hey! We didn't come
here to play, Squirt!
We came here to train!
Understand?!
[GOHAN] Now let's put our
noses to the grindstone
for a little while and get
some serious work done!
Okay?!
[GOTEN]
Aw...
[GOHAN]
Look!
I'm not trying to hurt
your feelings, Goten!
It's just that I
have work to do!
[GOHAN]
Mm! Hyaa!
Hyaaa!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOTEN]
Gohan!
What?! What now, Goten?! Aah!
[GOTEN]
I've got him, Gohan!
I've got the big one! Whoa!
Ha, ha, ha, ha! Woo!
[GOHAN]
Goten! Get down from there!
That's very dangerous!
[GOTEN laughs]
[GOHAN]
Aah! Goten! Haaaa!
Hey, are you okay?
[GOTEN] I just have
a bump on my head!
Don't you know you
coud've been killed?!
Are you crazy?!
Do you know how mad
Mom would've been
if I went home for dinner
and told her you were dead?!
Yes! Sorry! Gosh!
[GOHAN grunting]
Whew! Hm?
[GOHAN]
Goten!
Huh?!
I need your help, bro!
Can you assist me
in an exercise?
Yeah!
[GOHAN]
There! That oughta be enough!
Enough for what?
When are you gonna tell me
what we're doing?! Huh?!
[GOHAN] It's simple!
It's like playing a game!
You throw the rocks
and I dodge 'em?
'Kay?
[GOTEN] You want me to
hit you with the rocks?
[GOHAN] If you can!
But, you can't cross this line!
This is a great drill!
It sharpens intuitive reaction!
It teaches you how to act when
you don't have time to think!
[GOTEN]
Mm-hm! I get it now!
Alright, Goten!
Good! Let 'em fly!
[GOTEN]
Don't you think the line
should be a little
farther back, Gohan?
Nah! Don't worry about me!
I'll be just fine!
If anything, it's a
little too far back!
You must be fast! Wowee!
Well! We'll see!
Hopefully big brother
hasn't gotten too rusty!
[GOTEN]
Hmm... 'Kay!
I'm gonna throw
as hard as I can!
Great! Go!
[GOTEN]
Alright! Here it comes!
[GOHAN gasps]
Wow! I can't believe it!
You are fast!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOTEN]
Wow! This is fun, Gohan!
Let's do it some more!
[GOHAN]
No, no, no! Whoa!
Wait a second, Goten!
I think we are going to move
the line back a little bit!
There! That oughta do it!
Man, sport! That's a heck
of an arm you've got there!
Let's give it a try
from back here now!
[GOTEN]
Okay! Whatever you say! Haa!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOTEN laughing]
[GOHAN]
I'm getting used to it, Goten!
Keep 'em coming!
You can move in closer now!
[GOTEN]
Hm?
Uhh! Hey, why'd you stop, bro?
Well, since Mom's
not here is it okay
if I be like you now?
[GOHAN]
Hmm! Well...
What do you mean, like me?
[GOTEN] Well, you know!
The golden hair!
And the super strength!
I wanna be a Super Saiyan now!
[GOHAN laughs] Maybe when
you're a little older!
It takes years of training
to become a Super Saiyan!
I was twice your age
before I was strong enough
for Dad to teach me
how to transform!
Of course, I was the youngest
Super Saiyan ever!
You might need
more time! Huh?!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] Goten! You're a...
You're a Super Saiyan!
Oh, my gosh!
This is unbelievable!
[GOHAN]
Incredible! Whoa! Man!
When in the world did
this happen, Goten?!
This change-- s-since when?!
[GOTEN]
Mmm... I don't remember!
[GOHAN]
Ahh?! This is crazy!
You're such a natural,
Goten! My goodness!
Dad and I had to struggle really
hard to become Super Saiyans!
And Vegeta!
What a case he was!
So, How'd you like to be
my sparring partner, Goten?
Does that sound okay?
Yeah!
Do you know
sparring form, Goten?
Yeah, of course!
That's the one that
Mom always taught me
while you were studying!
I love that one!
Our Mom trained you?
Uh-huh! Everyday! While you
were doing homework!
[GOHAN]
Hmm?
[GOHAN thinking] Mom sure has
changed since the old days!
Even her letting me
out of school to train
for the tournament
is a huge difference!
I think that Dad dying must've
had a lot to do with it!
Hey, sport. Does, uh,
does Mom know about this?!
You know! About being able
to become a Super Saiyan?!
[GOTEN]
Mm-hm!
[GOTEN thinking]
Oh, yeah! She knows, alright!
[CHICHI grunting]
[CHICHI]
Come on, Goten! Counter!
Hey, you! Stop running
away and fight!
Hyaa!
Come on! Hyaaa! Huh?!
[CHICHI gasps]
[GOTEN yells]
[CHICHI yells]
[GOTEN] Huh?
[GOTEN]
Gosh, Mom! Are you okay?!
[CHICHI]
Huh?! You're a Su...
...per Saiyan!
[GOTEN]
I am? Is that bad?
Uuugh! Not another
monster in the family!
[GOHAN]
What's the matter, Goten?
Did Mom give you a hard time
when you transformed?!
Yeah! She said never
do it again!
I guess it's a bad thing because
she called me a monster!
[GOHAN laughs]
Don't worry about it too much!
You're the best
little monster I know!
[GOHAN] Alright, Goten!
Are you ready?!
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
[GOHAN]
Let's do it!
[GOHAN, GOTEN grunting]
Take this!
[GOTEN]
Huh?
Hey! That's not fair, Gohan!
[GOHAN]
Hm?
[GOTEN]
You're cheating!
You have to stay on the
ground because I can't fly!
What?! Are you kidding me?!
No! If I could fly,
I'd be kicking your butt!
Uh?! That's incredible! Wow!
That's like learning how
to run before you can crawl!
You're more like
a super-pedestrian
than a Super Saiyan!
A super what?!
Hey! Sorry, Squirt!
It's just that it's funny!
Funny?! Well, you better
teach me how to fly,
because I don't like
being laughed at!
You hear me?!
[GOHAN]
Whoa! Whoa! Easy there, Tiger!
Cut me some slack!
Alright! I'll teach you
how to fly, Goten!
How's that?
Wow! You will?!
[GOHAN]
Yes!
[GOTEN]
Ha, ha! Alright!
I'm gonna fly! I'm gonna fly!
[GOHAN laughing]
Hm! Hm?
Wait... is that...
...Videl?
Yikes! I'd almost forgotten!
Flying lessons!
I promised her at school that
I'd teach her how to fly!
[GOTEN]
Gohan! What's the matter?!
[GOHAN]
Uhh, nothing!
But it looks like you're
gonna have a partner
for the flying lessons!
A partner? Who?
It's a long story!
There's a girl in
my class and I promised
that I would
teach her how to fly!
And, she's heading for
our house right now!
She's gonna be your parnter
in the leassons but,
don't show her how strong
you really are, okay?
Uh, look! What I mean is...
Don't show her that you're
a Super Saiyan! Got it?
Oh, I see!
She's scared of
little monsters, isn't she?!
[GOHAN]
Uhh... Mm... Yeah!
I guess you could
say that, Goten! Come on!
Let's boogie!
[GOTEN]
Right!
Hey! You're really fast, Gohan!
I can't believe that
I couldn't hit you
with one of those rocks!
That was incredible!
Well, you've got a
real talent yourself!
I can't believe that
you're this far along!
Maybe you could enter the
World Championships too
if you keep practicing!
[GOTEN]
Are you serious?!
Me, enter the Worlds
Martial Arts Championship?!
That would be the
most awesome, incredible,
totally cool thing that could
ever happen to a kid my age!
Wow!
You know, I play fight
games with Trunks
all the time and he's
even stronger than I am!
What? Is he really?
That's amazing!
I had no idea that you
guys were even playing
these training games!
Yeah! It's a lot of fun!
That's all we do when
Bulma brings him over!
[GOHAN thinking]
Holy cow!
These little guys are gonna
get stronger than I am
if I don't watch it!
[CHICHI] Missy, whatever
it is you're selling,
I don't want it.
[VIDEL] Hi there!
I was looking for Gohan!
Is he home?
[CHICHI] Well, if you've
come looking for a date,
I'm afraid you've come
to the wrong place!
What manners you have!
Coming over unannounced and
without a proper introduction!
Shame on you!
Look, lady! I'm not
here for a date!
Sure! Huh?
[GOHAN]
Hi, Mom! We're back!
[VIDEL]
Hm?!
[GOTEN] Hey, Mom! I got
to throw rocks at Gohan!
[CHICHI]
You did?!
Well... Hi! Wow!
How'd you find
my address, Videl?!
Simple. I looked you up
in the Student Directory.
[GOHAN laughs]
Oh yeah...
Now! Listen up!
Thought you could
get out of our deal
by taking a leave of
absence from school?
Well, I've got news
for you, Gohan!
You're gonna teach
me how to fly!
That's fine!
I gave you my word and
that's all there is to it!
[CHICHI] Excuse me! My Gohan
can't give you lessons!
He's busy preparing himself
for the World Championships!
[GOHAN] Mom! Videl's actually
the one that talked me into
taking part in the
World Championships!
If it wasn't for her,
I would have never even
considered entering!
[VIDEL]
Hm!
[CHICHI] Hmm. Well,
alright then! Teach her!
But let me give you
some advice, young lady!
You keep your filthy
hands off my son!
[VIDEL growls]
Hey!
I've had enough of
your trashy talk, lady!
[CHICHI gasps]
Oh...
Guh...
[CHICHI] Alright! You listen
and you listen good!
Our family is counting
on the prize money
from this tournament to live on!
And the last thing we need
is for Gohan to be distracted
from his training
by a hussy like you!
Rrrrgh! I am not a hussy!
We're training for a Martial
Arts Tournament, not eloping!
The two don't mix!
My Mom and Dad got married
at the World Championships!
Didn't you, Mom?
Maybe that's why she's worried!
I guess kissy-kissy stuff
and fighting do mix sometimes,
don't they, Mom?!
In our case, yes! I competed!
I faught your Dad and married
him in the same day!
You faught in the Worlds...?
[CHICHI]
Ahhh! Those were the days!
Those were some of the
happiest times of my life!
Going head-to-head with
Goku in a vicious battle!
And then, riding off
with him, hand in hand,
in a swirl of romance that still
makes me tingle to this day!
It was the beginning of
our new life together!
Ah... Yes!
Sometimes true love
and fighting do mix!
But you! Your case is different!
Goku and I had been dating
since we were kids!
Look! I don't
wanna marry your son!
I wanna learn how
to fly! That's all!
Are you deaf or something?!
[CHICHI]
Rrrgh! How dare you!
[VIDEL growls]
[NARRATOR]
It's the Mother of all catfights
and this one could
go on until dawn!
But does Gohan have time to
waste with the commencement
of the World
Martial Arts Championship
just one month away?!
Oh, man!
Looks like those two are
really hitting it off!
[GOTEN laughs]
[GOHAN thinking] Goten really
does remind me of Dad!
So powerful and yet
so happy and carefree!
I wonder if he's gonna
be more powerful
than all of us someday?!
[GOHAN thinking] Just a child,
and he's already a Super Saiyan!
Man! Looks like
I've got work to do!
[NARRATOR]
As the battle between
Videl and Chichi continues,
the real battle approaches!
Will Goten be able to
enter the tournament?
And will Gohan have enough
time to get ready?!
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!