[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the planet Namek continued
to crumble apart
as King Kai hatched a plan
to restore Frieza's victims
back to life using a wish to the
Eternal Dragon of the Earth.
[NARRATOR]
Mr. Popo made the wish,
but it was a tall order,
even for an Eternal Dragon.
And the Dragon wasn't sure if it
could fulfill the wish or not.
[SHENRON] I... don't know.
[NARRATOR] Back on Namek,
the showdown continued
between the Super Saiyan Goku,
and Frieza, the evil tyrant.
The amazing Saiyan
continued to challenge
the depths of Frieza's
strength even though
the villain was at his
maximum power level.
[NARRATOR] Does Goku has
something up his sleeve?
He's going to need it, because
Frieza has committed himself
to an all-out attack!
[NARRATOR] The two super powers
are on a crash course.
Find out which one
survives, today!
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA yells]
[KING KAI] Oh, my!
[KING KAI grunts]
Holy cow!
What a jolt!
Ughhh... Knocked
my socks off!
My word...
This is truly a
battle like no other!
Kami?
Kami, we're running out of time!
What about the wish?
Yes, yes, of course.
Mr. Popo is on the job
as we speak.
The wish has been made.
But the Eternal Dragon is
having trouble fulfilling it.
Fulfilling this wish is no
simple task, my friend.
It's a big one!
[SHENRON growls]
My goodness...
[thinking] Dad..
I'm not leaving without you!
[BULMA whimpers]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] Oh my gosh!
Three minutes!
Gohan, the computer says
that this planet is going
to be history in three minutes!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
This is it!
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU] Huh?!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOHAN gasps]
It's over!
[BULMA] What?!
What do you mean "It's over"?!
My Dad's power signal...
I can't sense it...
Gone!
Wh-What does that mean?!
It means that...
That he's dead...
No! Hey!
That can't be!
[FRIEZA] I can't believe it!
This is incredible!
He's actually gone!
I did it! I won!
Yes!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] No one can beat me!
I am lord of the Universe!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[BULMA] I hate to say it, Gohan,
but if your Dad's been defeated,
then it's time to get the heck
out of here while we still can!
Gohan...?
[GOHAN] Piccolo...
[BULMA] Gohan, are you okay...?
I know it's hard,
but we gotta go.
[GOHAN] I'm staying, Bulma.
You're gonna have to
leave with Piccolo!
[BULMA] What?! Hey!
This isn't funny!
[GOHAN] I'm part Saiyan, Bulma.
Frieza is gonna hunt
me down wherever I go.
The last thing I wanna do
is lead him back to Earth.
I don't want to be
a danger to anybody...
I know what I've got to do.
That's nonsense!
Let's go!
You're not sure that he's
going to follow you.
We really should get out
of here before it's too late!
Gohan, no!
Don't go!
You can't put this
all on yourself!
Don't worry about me.
This is the way that I want it.
I'll be alright.
You take care of Piccolo.
[BULMA] Gohan, no!
This is suicide!
No way!
This is life.
Piccolo would understand.
And so would my Dad!
Besides, I don't
intend to die.
Frieza's bound to be hurting
if he was fighting my Dad.
Maybe I can beat him!
I've got to
give it a try!
So long!
[BULMA] Gohan, wait!
Gohan, come back!
Please don't leave me!
[CHICHI] I can't
take this anymore...
I think I'm losing my mind!
Gohan...
Please...
[ROSHI] Hey, ChiChi.
Take a break! Please!
Look, they're going to be fine.
When Goku's in control,
you really can't go wrong.
Mm-hm!
That's right! It's true!
Yeah, but...
Well, let's say that Goku wins
and beats this "Frieza" dude!
What good is that gonna
do if the planet blows up?
[DR. BRIEF yells]
So you think they're
going to die, do you?!
Well, let me tell you
something about my Goku!
He has never hurt anybody
in his entire life!
He's like an angel!
And angels don't die...
Do they...?
[CHICHI sobs]
[DR. BRIEF &amp; ROSHI sigh]
Oh.
Great Scott!
[VILLAGERS gasping]
How bizarre!
We're back, but is this a dream?
No way!
We're really alive!
But not for long!
This whole planet
is falling apart!
Why were we
brought back?
Just to die again?!
[DENDE] Huh...?
[DENDE] Oh, my gosh!
What's going on?!
So far, so good.
But where's Guru?
Huh?
The sky...
It's black.
Time to get out of here.
She's about to blow.
And I don't have enough energy
to weather the explosion.
Well, so long.
You fulfilled the legend,
only to become a fresh batch
of Super Saiyan Soup.
[FRIEZA laughs]
Huh?!
No, it can't be!
What?! It is!
Huh...?
Don't leave now.
It's not over yet!
Heh.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA laughs]
"Not over yet"?
That's a good one, kid.
You're a funny little guy.
You're just in time
for a quick beating.
Well... We'll see...
I think...
It's your turn!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
A pint-size Saiyan!
Hmph.
You don't really believe
that you can succeed
where both your father
and Vegeta failed?
Maybe you do
believe it!
It wouldn't surprise me to
know that the last Saiyan
to perish at my hands, was
just as foolish as the first.
Darn shame, isn't it?
A noble race like the
Saiyans completely extinct.
Or am I speaking too soon?
Perhaps you really are
going to strike me down.
Well... Let's find out!
Show me what you've got!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN yells]
Huh?!
Where are you going?
Don't tell me you've had a
change of heart, big guy?
Well, it's too late now,
you're going to have to learn
how to finish
what you've started.
This is one game that
we play to the end!
[GOHAN grunts]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA] Take that!
[FRIEZA] You're no fun!
All bark and no bite.
What a joke.
[thinking]
Just two more minutes...
If I can hold out for
two more minutes
he'll get caught
in the explosion...
Yes...
Your wish has been granted!
Many thanks!
[SHENRON] Fare
thee well!
[GURU groans]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] How did
I get back here?
It's impossible,
but I'm really alive!
Hey!
It worked! Super!
The Nameks! They're back!
[YAMCHA] Yeah!
But what about Guru?
Without him, it's no use!
He's the only one who
can make our plan work.
[KING KAI] You're right, Tien!
There's no cause to celebrate
if Guru hasn't returned.
Now, let's see...
Ahh...
The sky is dark...
That's a good sign!
Now, where are you, Guru?
Where are you...?
My goodness gracious.
I'm back!
And so are my children!
[PORUNGA roars]
It's a go!
Guru's back!
--Hah! Yes!
--Yaaay!
Hey, guys, time out! The wish!
Who's gonna make
your wish, King Kai?
That's right!
Are you going to find
someone to do it in time?
Have a little faith!
Hmm...
[KING KAI] Guru?
Guru, this is King Kai calling!
Can you hear me?
Yes, of course. Hi.
[KING KAI] Guru!
There's not much time!
I need to ask a favor of you!
[GOHAN yells]
[FRIEZA] Where to now, squirt?
Hmm...?
[GOHAN growls]
[thinking] Just a little longer!
H-Huh?!
[FRIEZA giggles]
Another push-over.
Just like your dad.
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN] You...
You jerk!
My, my!
So there's a little
spark left after all.
Since you have
a little energy left,
let me recommend a
course of action:
Beg for your life!
Just like your father
did before he died!
[GOHAN gasps]
That's right!
And he cried!
Just like a big baby!
It was sad!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN yells]
Ah!
Now he's ready to fight.
[GOHAN yells]
Huh?!
Darn kid!
What's he trying to do?
What?!
Hey!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA} You never
meant to fight.
You're trying to buy
some time, aren't you?
Transaction canceled!
You can't outsmart me.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] I'll be long gone
when this planet blows up!
And you? You will be dead!
Please..
Father, help...
Hmm...?
You're still there!
I feel it.
Please, Dad!
Help me!
[GOHAN growls]
You hurt my Dad!
You killed my friend!
[GOHAN yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[blows landing,
FRIEZA grunting]
[FRIEZA screams]
Masenko... Ha!
[GOHAN growls]
Magnificent
attack for a kid.
You are a true Saiyan.
Which is precisely why
I have to kill you.
It seems that I have become
the Saiyan exterminator.
It's a dirty job, but
somebody has to do it.
Tough luck!
But, hey, my hands are tied.
So...
[FRIEZA] This is the end
of the road for you, kid!
[FRIEZA pants]
[thinking] Father,
I-I'm sorry...
I really tried!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
It's time.
Huh?!
[GOHAN gasps]
What?!
Dad!
You're back!
Go! Now!
Huh?!
You were supposed
to leave the planet!
But... Daddy...
Go!
Right...
Win, Dad...
But how?! I killed you!
[NARRATOR] Goku has returned!
But there's not much time left.
The planet Namek
has reached its limits
and will explode any second.
Can King Kai's
plan work?
Who is going to make his
wish to the Dragon of Namek?
On the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!