[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
The demented Dr. Gero
escaped to his
mountain hideout to
carry out the final phase
of his evil plan.
The doctor, now
an android himself,
activated two more of his
mechanical monsters.
The first to awaken was
17, a black haired boy
with super strength
and intelligence.
Next out was 18, a
computer driven diva
with blonde hair
and a bad attitude.
Don't let their looks fool you!
They may appear
harmless, but these two
are programmed to
pulverize planet earth!
And while Krillin
and the others force
their way into
the secret lab,
Dr. Gero's about
to find out that
his menacing machines
have minds of their own.
[DR. GERO] Huh? Android 17!
What are you doing?
Then let's try another idea.
[DR. GERO]
What?! What have you done?
You dare to defy me?
I created you!
You're not going to put us
to sleep again, old man.
Rats! It's sealed shut!
[VEGETA] Out of the way!
I'll blast it open!
[ALL]
Huh?
Don't do it! We can't beat
the androids without Goku!
Stop it! You don't understand
how powerful they are!
Too late, kid!
[PICCOLO, KRILLIN gasp]
[VEGITA]
Well, well...
What have we here that
has you all so nervous?
A boy with long hair and
a scarf around his neck,
and a beautiful young girl...
I take it these are
the scary Androids
we've heard so much about?
That's them.
They're androids? They look
just like humans to me!
[TRUNKS] Don't be fooled
by the way they look.
They're both deadly!
And they're stronger
than all of us!
[DR. GERO]
Well...
Goku's friends are very
determined to stop us...
But they will not!
[DR. GERO]
We will destroy them
just as they
destroyed Android 19!
Android 19?
So you built him after all!
[DR. GERO]
Yes!
[ANDROID 17]
I see.
But he was of a different
design than 18 or myself.
He was an energy-absorbing
model, was he not?
[DR. GERO]
Yes, he was.
How very interesting.
And you've chosen that
same design for yourself?
You thought that an
energy-absorbing model like 19
would be easier to control?
Yes!
And now he's been destroyed!
[DR. GERO growls]
What are they up to?
[TIEN grunts]
[DR. GERO] That is enough
questions for now.
I order you to destroy
these intruders!
[ANDROID 17]
Be quiet old man!
We will deal with them
when we are ready.
What did you say?
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
[DR. GERO growling]
[DR. GERO] I really wish you
had not smashed the controller!
Ha!
[ANDROID 18]
Yes, that's too bad, isn't it?
[ANDROID 18] Planning to
use it for spare parts?
[DR. GERO]
Huh?
[ANDROID 18]
He's kind of lacking
in the looks
department, isn't he?
I'd like to see what
other modifications
you've made to him, Doctor!
[DR. GERO] You stay away from
there! Do not open that chamber!
I order you to stay
away from Android 16!
[TRUNKS] 16?! There's another
android I didn't know about?
Go on. I think it is time to
wake up our sleeping friend.
[ANDROID 18]
Right!
[DR. GERO]
No! Do not listen to him!
I have not completed
his programming yet!
What?
Something's not right, in there!
You got that right!
[KRILLIN] Guys! Now would
be a good time to attack!
Before they get
their act together!
Step aside! I don't need your
help to defeat these three!
[DR. GERO]
I must get control of them!
The 16 is just a prototype.
If you activate it,
it may malfunction.
[ANDROID 17 laughs]
Let's find out!
No, 18!
I think it's time to send
you to the scrap heap!
[DR. GERO groans]
[ANDROID 18]
Now, where was I?
[DR. GERO growls]
[ANDROID 18]
If 16 is just a prototype,
I wonder why you've
kept him for so long?
You destroyed all the other
androids up to 15, didn't you?
[DR. GERO] I was planning
to repair him someday!
Listen, I made you,
and I am telling you that if you
activate 16, you will regret it!
We will regret it?
I doubt that, old man.
[DR. GERO]
Huh?
According to this data,
I am much stronger
than this model is!
It makes no difference!
Hm. 18, go ahead
and activate him. Now.
I am your creator! You will
do as I tell you to do!
[DR. GERO] Stop meddling
with Android 16 now!
Or I will force you to stop.
[ANDROID 17]
Your controller is broken!
Then I will make another!
Hm.
For the last time!
Do not release him!
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[DR. GERO groans]
[KRILLIN, TIEN gasp]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
[TRUNKS growls]
What have you done?
How dare you?
Don't you know?
I gave you life!
And I can take it away!
[DR. GERO groans]
[DR. GERO grunting]
[KRILLIN yelping]
That does it!
Now I am mad!
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[TRUNKS grunts]
Did you see that?
He squashed him like a bug!
[ANDROID 17 clears throat]
[KRILLIN] Uh, Vegeta? I think
he wants to talk to you.
[ANDROID 17] You with the
shiny head. Come here.
[KRILLIN gasps]
You talking to me?
[KRILLIN yelps]
No way! Not me!
[ANDROID 17 laughs]
[VEGETA] Don't be a coward!
[VEGETA]
Go on, fight him!
[KRILLIN] All by myself? Come on
guys, we're in this together!
I'd like to keep my
head on my shoulders.
Don't worry about it.
I've got you covered, Krillin.
[TIEN, KRILLIN gasp]
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
[KRILLIN sighs]
It looks like he took
pity on you, loser!
That's too bad.
You're so pathetic.
Now he knows you're scared.
[VEGETA] Next time he won't
show you any mercy at all!
What?
[ANDROID 17]
Open the chamber!
If they set that android free,
it will be the end of all of us!
[TRUNKS]
No!
[TRUNKS yells]
[KRILLIN]
Get down!
[KRILLIN sighs]
[KRILLIN]
Hey Trunks!
How about a little more warning
the next time you do that?!
[VEGETA grunts]
Bad move.
What'd you go and do that for?
[TRUNKS]
What's wrong?
Well, look! Down there!
[TRUNKS]
I don't understand.
There's no way anyone
could survive that!
That was my most intense blast!
[VEGETA]
Looks like you spoke too soon!
[TRUNKS gasps]
Now, that's too bad!
By doing that,
You just showed them
how weak you are!
Don't make me wait all day, 18.
Are you going to
open it up or not?
Never let a boy
do a man's job.
[TRUNKS grunting]
[ANDROID 18]
Let's meet our new friend!
Oh, no, they did it!
Great. Now we'll have
to fight another one!
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
[ANDROID 16 grunting]
Uh, guys? He's, uh,
big! He's very big!
And he's ugly too!
[TRUNKS growls] I didn't know
Dr. Gero made another android!
How could I have missed one?
Well, good morning.
It must feel good to
get out of that coffin.
How long have you been cooped up
in that container for, anyway?
Come on, speak. Did Dr. Gero
not give you a voice box?
He tried to tell us it was
dangerous to activate you.
Why would he say such
a thing? Do you know?
Do you have something to say?
Hello, anybody home in there?
[ANDROID 17]
The strong, silent type, huh?
Come on. Let's go!
Where to?
To complete our mission.
Are you with me, 18?
16, Dr. Gero programmed you
with a mission to destroy Goku.
Isn't that right?
[ANDROID 16]
That's right!
I'll be. So, the big guy
can speak after all!
Dr. Gero must have
programmed him to react
only to commands that
relate to his main objective.
[ANDROID 17] I didn't think
the doctor was that smart,
but let's see if 16 can
carry out his objective:
find Goku and destroy him!
[ANDROID 17]
Let's get outta here!
[KRILLIN]
Hey! They're leaving!
[VEGETA growling]
Good riddance. We're safe!
But, where do you
think they're going?
Should we follow them?
If they went that
direction they're not going
to South City.
That's the other way!
I've got it! They've
gone after Goku.
Yeah. Dr. Gero's goal
was to get back
at Goku for destroying
his Red Ribbon Army!
Yeah, but, do you still
think those androids
will follow Dr. Gero's
orders now?
[VEGETA growling]
I don't care where they went.
I'll track them down myself!
They're cowards.
They left because they
were afraid of me.
And they should be!
[TRUNKS]
No! Stop!
Stay here! Don't go after them!
You expect me to
wait for Kakarot?
Kakarot? Oh, you mean Goku?
That's right! We need
him for this battle!
[TRUNKS] We're only strong
enough if we all stay together.
[VEGETA laughs]
Sure, let's wait for Kakarot!
I mean wouldn't it be easier
if we all just joined up
with the androids
instead? He's history!
[TRUNKS growls]
[VEGETA] Now get out of my
way before you get hurt!
And let me finish
them off, by myself,
without Kakarot!
You can't!
If you face the androids alone,
you will be destroyed for sure!
[TRUNKS] You must
listen to me. Stay here!
[TRUNKS groans]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[VEGETA]
Now, stay out of my way!
[TRUNKS groans]
[KRILLIN]
What was that all about?
[TIEN]
Trunks!
[KRILLIN]
Are you okay?
Please, stop him!
We have to wait until Goku gets
better, or we're all doomed!
We must wait!
[TRUNKS]
Go after him!
But, Vegeta's long gone.
We'll never catch up to him now!
Darn it! I sure wish
Goku was here!
Goku...
We have to go after him!
There's no time to waste!
[BABY babbling]
[BULMA cooing]
[YAJIROBE]
My scarf, a diaper for that kid!
That's just great!
What could be worse?
[BULMA]
Yajirobe!
Hurry up with the
diaper, would ya!
Just a minute!
Do you want poor little
Trunks here to catch a cold?
[YAJIROBE]
Hey, Don't worry,
we know he grows up
to be big and strong!
Yeah, that is true.
That's right!
You're gonna grow up
to be a big boy!
[BABY laughing]
[BULMA]
That's a good boy!
That's right!
Yajirobe has your pants!
[BULMA cooing]
[GOHAN] Bulma, I'm ready
to go home anytime you are.
Oh, sure.
I guess you want to get
home and see your Dad.
Let's go.
[BABY giggling]
[GOHAN] I hope he's
feeling better by now.
Dad, I'm thinking of you!
[CHICHI humming]
If I know my Goku,
the first thing
he's going to say
when he feels better is,
"ChiChi, I'm starving!"
[CHICHI] So, I'm gong to
whip up something special,
because he's going to pull
through any minute now,
I just know he will!
[GOKU screaming]
[YAMCHA]
Goku!
Hang on. Here take this!
[CHICHI]
Goku?
[GOKU panting]
He's in pain!
Don't worry, ChiChi,
Goku will pull through.
He's the toughest guy I know and
no disease can slow him down.
He'll be back on
his feet in no time.
[CHICHI]
I hope you're right.
[YAMCHA] I think the medicine
is working! He looks better now.
Do you think so?
[YAMCHA] Piccolo said Goku's
disease could be contagious.
So, I'm going to take
some of this medicine.
I think you'd better
take some too!
Okay. But you buy your own!
Uh-- Come on! You know
I'm good for it.
And I can pay you
back next week!
[VEGETA] Why is everybody
making such a big deal
about Kakarot?
Who needs him anyway?
Have they forgotten
that I'm a Saiyan too?
A Saiyan from
a royal bloodline?
Well soon they will see
how powerful I really am!
[BIRDS chirping]
[ANDROID 18]
Is something wrong?
[ANDROID 17]
No, don't blow a circuit.
I just wanted to enjoy the
scenery from down here.
[ANDROID 18]
So we walk?
No, we drive.
We're going to take the next
automobile that passes by us.
So, how does that sound?
Hm. It sounds to me like
you're being foolish.
17, why should we waste
our time driving a car?
Because we've never
done it before.
We're planning on taking
a little car ride, 16.
[ANDROID 17]
Do you wanna go too?
What? Did you just say "Goku"?
I guess I'll take
that as a "yes".
Seems Goku is the only
thing he has on his mind.
[ANDROID 17]
Hm. That's strange.
It seems Dr. Gero
created 16 without
any of the human personality
traits that 18 and I have.
I'll be curious to
see what other flaws
he has in his design.
[VEGETA]
So, there you are!
[VEGETA] I didn't think
you'd be this easy to find.
Run out of gas?
[ANDROID 17] There's
something different about you.
What happened?
I'm showing my true self.
I'm the most powerful
being on this planet!
And you're not welcome here!
[ANDROID 18] You're quite
brave for someone all alone!
Don't worry. I came prepared!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] I'm going to put
you back in the crates
you crawled out of!
[BOTH chuckle]
You're laughing? Why is
that? This is not a joke!
Tell me, are all
of you Saiyans so
full of yourselves?
Is Goku like you?
Is this the way you try
to hide your incompetence?
[ANDROID 17] We androids will
always be superior to your kind!
You take that back!
You'll regret saying that!
You're nothing but a
machine made of tin!
You're just a bunch of toys
made by a crazy old man!
And don't forget that
tin toys can be broken!
He talks too much.
What was that?
[ANDROID 18]
16! Let's see what you can do!
Destroy him!
I refuse.
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
So, the big guy's not so dumb,
huh? Now, who's it going to be?
[ANDROID 17]
He refuses?
Who does he think he is?
[ANDROID 18]
Never mind him.
I'll handle this.
Ready? Little man?
[VEGETA]
So, it's ladies first, is it?
That's fine with me!
Now, don't expect me
to go easy on you.
I fight to win!
[NARRATOR]
Android 18 looks like she's one
tough customer, but
is she strong enough
to go one on one
with a Super Saiyan?
Whatever the outcome
Vegeta has got his
hands full with these
three bionic brutes.
Is he ready to battle
these mechanical monsters
all by himself?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!