[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z...
With his father's help,
Gohan was able to tap
into his deepest powers
and finally destroy
the monstrous Cell.
[NARRATOR] After years
of turmoil caused by
Dr. Gero's Androids, the Earth
was brought back to normal...
Except for one thing...
[NARRATOR]
Goku could not be revived
by the powers of
the Earth's Dragon...
And despite a clever plan to
bring him back to life,
Goku decided it'd be safer for
the Earth if he didn't return.
[NARRATOR] And so,
friends and family were forced
to say goodbye to the
Saiyan they had for so long
called their own...
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
light years above,
along the winding
track of Snake Way,
Goku was adjusting well to
life in the Other World.
[GOKU laughs]
[BUBBLES chatters]
[GREGORY yells]
[GREGORY] You take
that side, Bubbles!
[GREGORY &amp; BUBBLES yell]
[NARRATOR] As Goku went to
recess with Bubbles and Gregory,
King Kai toiled away at
building a replacement
for his exploded home.
But, well, that
didn't work...
[GOKU] Oh, man. Sorry, King Kai!
Gosh, I really blew it.
I feel so dumb!
No... No, it's
not true, Bubbles...
[GREGORY] Come on, Bubbles!
[BUBBLES chatters]
[NARRATOR] Now, Goku and
King Kai have started down
the endless miles
of Snake Way.
Next stop-- the
master of Other World!
[GREGORY hums,
BUBBLES chatters]
[GOKU] Now, up the hill!
Heave-ho! Heave--
[KING KAI] Hey, Goku! Come on!
Knock it off for a second
would ya?! My feet are
really killing me here!
You see-- I'm not
the running type!
[GOKU] Keep. It. Going. Ha, ha,
alright! Keep going, 1-2, 1-2.
Oh, yeah, yeah, keep going.
[BUBBLES gibbers]
--[KING KAi sighs]
--[GOKU] Whoa!
I forgot how long
Snake Way was!
Listen, uh, King Kai?
Can't you run any faster?
We're not making very good time.
How many times
can I say this?
We can't make bad time here
'cause in this world,
time never runs out!
But I still can't wait to see
this Master of Other World!
Talk about the ultimate
fighting challenge!
[KING KAI] I have
to tell you, Goku.
You better not think
lightly of him
or you're gonna
be in trouble.
Oh, I don't think
lightly of the guy.
I'm sure he's tough!
What?! "Guy"?!
You rude child!
How dare you call him "guy"!
You must call him by his
proper name so repeat after me!
His name is Grand Kai!
His name's Grand Kai...
The ruler of this world.
[GOKU] The ruler of thi--
[KING KAI] Quiet!
Now as you know, I am
King Kai, and watch over Earth
and your part of space
from high above.
But the Universe is
divided into four quadrants:
North, South, East, and West,
each with its own Kai.
But further above us
is the Grand Kai.
He is our ruler.
And to add more
kittens to the litter,
he's also a great Martial
Artist and his home's become
an eternal training ground for
heroic fighters who, like you,
have been allowed to keep
their bodies after death.
Wow! Are you serious?
Well, if there's other fighters
there too, I can't be late!
--[KING KAI screams]
--[GOKU] See ya later, King Kai!
[KING KAI screaming]
Hey, guys!
[screaming continues]
That's right I can... fly!
[KING KAI laughs]
Oh! Ooh.
Now I feel kind of silly
'cause I was in such a rush
I forgot to ask you how
to get to that place!
To reach the Grand Kai's
planet you must take a plane.
Got it! Thanks a lot!
[GOKU] Bye, guys!
He's like a big yo-yo.
I give him 2 more seconds...
Here he comes!
[GOKU] Hi, guys!
Sorry, I forgot to ask you
where the plane is!
[KING KAI] It's docked next
to King Yemma's castle
It's called the "Higher Plane."
"Higher Plane."
Right, got it. Bye!
Bye, guys!
You know, Goku would
be great material...
for my next standup routine.
[KING KAI laughs]
[shoes squeal]
--[GOKU laughs]
--[KING KAI] Ooh?
I just realized it'd be a lot
faster to get there this way!
[KING KAI grunts]
Goku! Hold on!
[cheering, whooping]
[DEVIL GUY A] Stay in line!
No pushing now!
You will all get your turn!
[KING YEMMA] You have passed...
[SPIRIT] I passed! I passed!
Oh yeah! It's gonna be awesome!
So awesome! I know it! Yeah!
Next...
Can I get the next
soul, please?
[GOKU] Hello!
Well, what do we have here?
Our old friend Goku!
Dead again already,
huh? And King Kai?!
How in the world did you die?
Well um, that's sort
of a long story...
[GOKU] Nice to see you
again, King Yemma!
Gotta jet!
You sure? Uh, would you
like a cup of tea, or uh...
Hey, stop! Sir, you
can't come this way!
I'm afraid you'll have to
stand in line like every--
Oh?
[DEVIL GUY B gasps]
Ah! You still have your body!
Huh...?
I haven't worked here long,
and you're the first one I've
ever seen, but can I just say...
You are an inspiration!
Uh...?
After you, sir!
[GOKU] Uh... Thank you...
That boy needs to be on a leash!
Or something...
Well, King Yemma, I'm off!
Alright. Have a nice trip!
[BUBBLES gibbers]
They've let him keep his body
and train with the Grand Kai...
He must have done
something incredible!
Huum...
"Rescued Earth
from evil Android"...
Works for me!
[SPIRITS cheer]
Hey! If you're in Group A
would you please follow me
and don't forget to show me
your boarding pass!
You! Yeah!
I said single file!
Now just keep your eye
on the person ahead of you
so no one
gets lost, okay?
[SPIRITS] O-kaaayyy!
--[BUBBLES chatters]
--[GREGORY] Bye-bye!
[GOKU] Man... How come we got
stuck with this old klunker
of a plane...?
Aww... I really wanted to ride
the big and fancy one...
Huh?
Whoa!
So this is the outer world!
It sure looks big!
[KING KAI] Well, you better
get your fill of it.
We're about to land.
[GOKU] Already? But where?
[KING KAI] There!
That's the one.
[GOKU] Where? I
don't see anything!
[KING KAI]
Straight ahead, ya' goof!
That's the Grand Kai's planet!
[GOKU] Oh! Gee,
doesn't look like much...
[KING KAI] Watch your mouth!
Oh, sorry! Guess it is
bigger than your planet.
Especially now!
[KING KAI gasps]
[KING KAI] Goku...
You are a rude, rude man.
Wow, this place is a
dream come true, King Kai!
Look at all these fighters!
Hey, King Kai!
Hey!
It's been a long time.
Good to see you, sir!
Yes! Training hard, guys?
[FIGHTERS] Yes sir!
Hey! I'd say you sure are famous
here in Other World aren't you?
Well, just with people
from the North Quadrant.
So... he's from where I'm from?
Sure, same Galaxy, but he's
about 2000 years your senior.
Oh... Two thousand years...
What?! Two thousand years?!
But... he's been training
himself for that long?!
Four million and one...
[KING KAI] So,
this is the place!
Not too shabby from
the ground, now is it, Goku?
[GOKU] Yeah, it's alright--
But where's the owner?
I've got to see him.
The strongest man in
Other World, whatshisname.
You'll address him
as the Grand Kai!
Keep talking like that
and you'll be up a creek!
'Cause he's that strong?!
This Big Kai?
Grand Kai!
Grand Kai...
That sounds much better, Goku.
You know, in all these years,
not even I have had
the privilege of seeing
the Grand Kai fight.
[GOKU] Really?
[KING KAI] But it is said that
no words can exactly describe
how forcefully, how beautifully,
and how absolutely terrifyingly
the Grand Kai fights.
[GOKU] Wow...
[KING KAI screams]
Oh! This is the one I
wanted! Mint condition!
Should've known he
had one! Look at her!
Whoa! Sweet!
Classic Chrome Detail!
Real Leather Interior!
Check out those fins! It's
cool! It's sleek! It's SEXY!
--[KING KAI moans]
--Ah, please, King Kai.
Can we go in now?
[VOICE] You! It's you!
[KING KAI] Hmm? Who's me?
Well, if it isn't West Kai!
[BOTH growl]
[GOKU gasps]
[growling continues]
Hold on!
Two Kais?! That's weird!
Whadda ya think
you're doing here?!
Take a guess!
[WEST KAI] Hmph! I hope it's
not to see the Grand Kai
'cause we have an
appointment!
As you must know, Pikkon
here is the prize fighter
of the West Quadrant!
The Grand Kai called
for him specifically!
[WEST KAI laughs]
Huh?
[KING KAI] Huh? What's wrong?
[WEST KAI] Hmm...
What?! Stop staring!
--[WEST KAI screams]
--[KING KAI screams]
[WEST KAI laughs]
What?!
[laughing continues]
You really are dead!
[KING KAI gasps]
Yeah, so what?!
The North Kai is dead!
[WEST KAI laughs]
After all your corny jokes,
it's 'bout time you WERE funny!
[WEST KAI laughs]
How dare you call my jokes
corny, you little shrimp!
I was involved in
something very important!
--[WEST KAI wheezes]
--That's right, sir.
King Kai saved my whole planet.
Hmm?!
Excuse me, who's this guy?
I'm Goku! It's nice to meet you!
Goku is a righteous fighter
who's saved his side
of the galaxy many times!
He's an incredibly strong guy!
Oh, "incredibly strong" you say?
Well... Surely you're
not suggesting
he's as strong as
my Pikkon...
[KING KAI] No...
Goku is stronger.
Oh? Do you have any idea
what you are suggesting?
Yes! That Goku is stronger!
Impossible! No one is
stronger than Pikkon!
Well, Goku is!
I don't believe you!
Fine then I'll prove it!
--[GOKU gasps]
--Uhh...?
You're on, big boy!
[GOKU] Huh...?
Now! Get him, Goku!
Wait! You want us
to fight right here?!
He's afraid! Take him
out quick, Pikkon!
--[OLD VOICE] Hold on!
--[WEST KAI] Huh?
[KING KAI gasps]
That must be...!
[KING KAI &amp; WEST KAI]
The Grand Kai!
Where is he?
Goku! You have to bow
or else he's gonna...
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH scream]
[coughing]
[music plays]
Hey!
Hail, Grand Kai!
[music plays]
[GRAND KAI] Uh-huh, mmm, yeah.
Daddy like it. Mmm-mmm-mm!
[music plays,
GRAND KAI hums]
[GOKU] This is the Grand Kai?!
[music plays,
GRAND KAI hums]
[GRAND KAI] Mm-hmm.
Sorry to walk in on
you guys like this.
Listen, Pikkon:
I need you to go
straight to Hell for me.
[PIKKON] Yes, sir...
That's... not very nice...
He's the Grand Kai!
He can say what he wants!
Now quiet!
You see, they're havin' a
bit of trouble down in Hell.
[ALL] Some trouble?
Yeah, King Yemma sent some
dufus named Cell down there
the other day and he's
gotten out of hand.
What?! Cell?!
Now down you go!
[CELL gasps]
[CELL screams]
Then someone called Frieza
and these other guys
joined him and they're
all running wild and stuff!
Frieza?!
He never quits!
[GRAND KAI] So, Pikkon,
I want you to run down there
and take care of 'em.
[PIKKON] Yes, of course...
[ALL] Huh?!
You'll need some help!
I'm coming with you!
[KING KAI] Wait! That's
not your call to make!
[GRAND KAI]
Play it cool, North Kai.
Might as well let him go. He
knows what he's doing, I guess.
Uhh...
I didn't ask you for
your assistance.
Yeah, but I've already fought
against both Cell and Frieza
and you haven't.
And unless you're something
crazy, you're gonna need help.
[GOKU]
This place is a mess.
Huh?!
[GOKU] Here we go...
[GOZ &amp; MEZ grunt]
Oh! Please don't hurt us!
We'll do whatever you tell us!
Please!
[GOKU] Hey! Don't worry, Pikkon,
it's only Goz and Mez.
Say, you're the one who
fell off of Snake Way!
Name's Goku!
[GOZ &amp; MEZ] Oh, good!
We thought you were Cell's men!
Actually... We're on our
way to take care of Cell!
[BOTH] Oh! Thank goodness!
[grunting]
[CELL] There has to be
a way out of here,
and you are going
to tell me it!
Because if you don't,
I'll have to torture you
and your petty friends
for the rest of eternity!
You are going to tell me! Now!
Auggh! I...
don't...
know...!
[CELL] Well then!
[CELL chuckles]
You know what that makes you...?
Expendable!
Noooo!
[CELL] Hm?!
[GOKU] It's sad! Even in
death you refuse to learn!
--[CELL laughs]
--It's Goku!
That's right, Frieza,
I'm stopping you again!
Oh, but now...
The odds are stacked
in my favor!
Seven to One is good odds.
Wouldn't you say, boys?
[GINYU FORCE]
Yeah!
[GINYU FORCE yells]
Pikkon! Catch!
[GOKU yells]
[GINYU FORCE yells]
[GOKU grunts]
--[GOKU yells]
--[BURTER grunts]
[RECOOME gasps]
I do say!
How... did he...
improve so much?!
[CELL] Don't you worry!
He'll soon be dealt with.
I'm the one who
killed him, remember?
Well... who said
we were worried?
After you, my friend...
[CELL] You're too kind...
What the--?!
[CELL gasps]
[CELL screams]
[GOKU gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[CELL yells]
Who's that?!
[GOKU] Pikkon...
He moves... so fast!
[KING COLD gasps]
[KING COLD yells]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[KING COLD whimpers]
[GINYU FORCE &amp; CELL scream]
[CELL screams]
[screaming continues]
This stinks...
They could at least
let us take showers...
[RECOOME] Does anybody
want to arm wrestle?
[ALL] Shut up!
[GOKU] Well, I was
wrong about one thing.
You didn't need help!
No... But thanks.
[NARRATOR] Even in Other World,
Goku is still saving the day!
And making a few new
friends in the process.
There's a big new
world ahead of him
with infinite time to explore!
And it looks like Goku
will do just that.
Stay tuned for more
of Dragon Ball Z!