[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
much to the dismay of Bulma,
the training continued
and took precedence over all!
[NARRATOR] A new World
Championship Tournament
was about to begin
and the contenders
were coming to the fore!
Grandpa! I just flew around
the world again! Good, huh?
Yeah! I think that was
your fastest time yet, Pan!
Think I'll be ready
for tomorrow then?
[NARRATOR] Were the tough
teenagers being upstaged
by the tenacious toddler?
And who was the mystery fighter
that Goku had gotten wind of?
Someone so powerful
that even he was looking
forward to the challenge!
No, I think this
guy is really shrewd.
We may have
ourselves a challenge.
[GOTEN]
Get out of here!
That girl over there?
I don't believe you!
[TRUNKS]
No! I'm serious!
We're going out tonight
after the tournament!
[CAPTAIN CHICKEN]
Buck, baawk! Buck baawk!
[UUB thinking]
Gosh! I didn't realize
there were so many
people in this world!
[KNOCK]
Hey, kid!
[UUB shrieks]
Relax!
Sorry!
[KNOCK]
Sorry, huh?
Well, don't be! So tell me!
How did a little twerp like you
make it past the preliminaries?
Maybe I was
just lucky, I guess.
Heh! Happens every time!
Every tournament there's
a few little squirts
that make it to the finals!
The funny thing is,
that one there makes
you look like a giant!
Oweee! Ow!
[WILD TIGER]
Did you do that?
I think you did. Didn't you?
Ohhh... I see.
Messin' with Wild Tiger?
Well, that's not
too smart. Dumb kid.
[chuckles]
[PAN sobs]
Grandpa!
Hahahaha!
[GOKU]
Hmm?
Hey, Pan. Don't cry.
It's just a game.
[ANNOUNCER] All right! It's
time to get the ball rolling!
The fighters will now draw lots
to see who will be matched up
with whom in the first round
of the finals!
This is a single-match
elimination tournament,
which means that
the losers go home
and the winners will
move on to the next round!
The winner of the final round
will proceed to the
Championship Match!
There he or she will
have the honor of competing
for the World Title
against the reigning
Champion of the World:
Mr. Satan!
Hey! Do you think the amazing
guy your dad was going on about
is really one of these?
Huh?
[TRUNKS]
They all seem kind of normal!
Yeah, well, there's one
of them that's not so normal!
Come on! Which
one is it, Kakarot?
Nope! Not tellin'!
[ANNOUNCER]
Now then! Fighters!
As I call your name, please
come up and draw a number!
The first fighter is Goten!
That's me!
Well, come on up!
[GOKU]
Hey, Buu!
[BUU]
Hmm?
I'd like you to
do me a little favor,
but you're gonna
have to use your magic.
[BUU]
Hmm?
Listen! I want you to
change the lot numbers
so I can fight this certain guy!
Will you do it?
Ahh! Okay! Buu do!
It's not like you to
break the rules, Kakarot!
I know! But I want to fight
this guy in the first round!
That way we'll both be
at one hundred percent
and it'll be a
totally fair match!
[GOTEN]
Here goes nothing!
[ANNOUNCER] Eight!
Goten has drawn number eight!
And the next fighter
to draw is Wild Tiger!
Yeah! Let me at
those numbers! Mmmm! Uhhh!
Come to Wild Tiger,
you little, round rascals!
[BULMA] Whoa! I wouldn't want
to be matched up with that guy!
[ANDROID 18] Aah! He's nothing!
Just a paper tiger!
Even Krillin could
beat a guy like that!
[KRILLIN] Oh well, thanks a lot!
That's a heck of a thing to say!
[ANDROID 18]
Well, you should have entered.
You might have
won some prize money.
Even I could have
been the World Champion
if I hadn't let Mr. Satan win.
Yeah, well what about Goku
and Vegeta withdrawing that year
to go fight Majin Buu!
Pan entered!
You're just a whimp!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Man! She's harsh!
Look! Pan's gonna
go pick a number, Mom!
Here she comes! The youngest
fighter in the tournament!
Now which one will it be?
Is it time for Buu
to use his sneaky magic?
[GOKU]
Not yet, Buu!
Yes! Number One!
Young Pan has picked Number One!
One! Then Pan's
gonna fight Two!
Which fighter is Number Two?
What? Holy smoke!
Pan's fighting that
gorilla, Wild Tiger!
[PAN] Number One!
Number One! Number One! Yay!
Hmph!
And the next fighter
to draw is Goku!
Let's do it!
[GOKU thinking]
Hmm! There's an open bracket!
[GOKU]
Buu! Make mine Number Three!
Okay!
Hi!
Long time no see!
The competitions just haven't
been the same without you, Goku!
It's good to be back!
[ANNOUNCER] Three!
Goku has picked Number Three!
And the next fighter
to draw is Narig!
Cool.
All right, Buu! Let's see!
Give this guy Number Six!
Six! Yes!
Hey! Hey! Is this guy the one?
It's Six! Narig
has picked Number Six!
Now! Uub! You're next!
Yes! Right!
All right, Buu!
Now make this one Number Four!
I don't care about
the rest of them!
Okay!
What? No way! That
can't be him! He's a kid!
[GOKU] He's been waiting
a long time for this!
Don't be deceived
by his appearance!
He's the one all right!
How could you possibly know
that? I don't understand!
Well, it's strange!
But right before I destroyed
the evil final form of Buu
I made a request!
I asked him to come
back as a good person
so we could fight together!
Apparently, King
Yemma heard my request
and decided to make it happen!
Wait? Hold on! You're
saying that this boy is Buu?!
Mm-hmm! I'm almost certain!
And there's a
pretty significant clue!
Just, look at his name!
It's U-U-B!
That's Buu spelled
backwards! Bizarre, huh?
Uub is final form
of Buu reincarnated!
Did you hear that?
Yes! It's crazy!
[UUB thinking] Ooo... I'm afraid
that what Mother said is true!
Even though I'm the strongest
one in my village there may be
some men in this world that
are even stronger than me!
Ohh! These men
look so powerful!
[VEGETA]
Twelve!
[UUB thinking] Oh, Heaven
help me! What am I gonna do?
I promised everyone
that I would win the prize
and come back with lots of food!
I can't go back empty handed!
[UUB thinking]
Goku... Which one is he?
Uh-oh!
The first round
match ups are now final!
[ANNOUNCER] In the first bout,
Pan will be facing Wild Tiger!
In the second bout,
Goku will take on Uub!
In the third bout, Narig
will fight Captain Chicken!
Next, Buu will face
Goten in the fourth bout!
The fifth bout will feature
Trunks and Otokoski!
And in the sixth, Vegeta will
go head to head with Knock!
[crowd cheers]
Fighters, the judges are gonna
need a few minutes to get ready,
and then we'll call the
names for the first bout!
Until then,
you are free to rest,
warm up, or do as you please
to prepare. Good luck to you!
Great! How come I'm the one
stuck fighting Buu
in the first round?
That's the luck of the draw!
Well! You'll
be on that date
a little sooner than
you thought, tough guy!
[WILD TIGER] Huh! What are
you bozos belly-aching about?
I have to fight
a little, bitty kid!
The mighty Wild Tiger doing
battle with a toddler? Come on!
Ahh! This is stupid!
They shouldn't even let you in!
This isn't a tournament
for breast-feeding babies!
[OTOKOSKI] Well,
I'm happy with my match-up!
Yum! Mmm! I'll be gentle
with you. Don't worry.
Yep! That's the luck
of the draw, Trunks. Hahaha.
[KNOCK] Hey! Old man, looks like
we'll be fighting each other.
Got a little attitude
there. Is that it?
Or are you just so old and ugly
that you can't hear anymore!
Hey! Hahahaha!
Hahahaha!
[VEGETA] Tell the officials my
opponent has decided to forfeit!
Ugh! Couldn't he wait?
Wow! Papa's strong!!
[ANNOUNCER]
And now for the moment
you've all been waiting for,
It's time to begin
the final rounds of the
World Martial Arts Championship!
[ANNOUNCER] Twelve fighters
are still remaining,
but only one of them
will earn the right to fight
for the title of World Champion
and the prize money
that goes with it!
Serving as the sponsor for
our prize money this year
is none other than Mr. Satan,
the reigning World
Champion, himself!
[WILD TIGER]
This just ain't right!
[VIDEL] All right!
It's almost time, sweety!
Let's get this good and tight!
There you go! Now be strong,
but also be careful, okay?
'Kay!
Stay loose, Pan!
Remember your training, okay!
Right!
[ANNOUNCER] Will Pan and Wild
Tiger please report to the ring?
[GOHAN]
You're on, Pan!
[VIDEL]
Go get 'em, sweetie!
[PAN]
Yeah!
Wish me luck!
[PAN] Bye, everybody!
Number one! Number one...
[GOKU]
Bye, Pan! I'll be watching!
[ANNOUNCER] In this first bout,
Wild Tiger is facing Pan,
a talented, young girl
at the tender age of four!
But don't be surprised,
her grandfather is none
other than the one, the only...
You got it! Mr. Satan!
It's time to go, go, go!
Are you ready
for the big show?
Yeah! Then allow me to
introduce the fighters!
First! The enormous
Wild Tiger and Pan!
She's so cute!
You go girl!
Careful there,
big guy! Ha, ha, ha!
[WILD TIGER thinking] So this is
the Champ's granddaughter, huh?
So what? It's still
embarrassing as heck! Munchkin!
Look man, I know she's
Hercules's granddaughter,
but how in the world did
she survive the preliminaries?
Uh, I got a feeling like this
could get really, really ugly!
[MR. SATAN] My poor, little Pan!
Please be okay!
Give it your best, Pan!
Pan! Take it easy on him, 'kay?
Go, Pan! You're the best!
Fighters! Let the match begin!
Yeah! All right!
So be it then!
Ohohoho!
Yay!!
[ANNOUNCER] Ah! What an attack!
At least he's still breathing!
The winner of the first bout,
by knockout, the mighty Pan!
[BULLA]
Way to go, Pan!
[OX-KING]
That's a girl, Pan!
[ANNOUNCER] And Pan
advances to the second round!
Number one! Number one! Yay!
Pan, you okay?
Uh, huh! Of course I am, Gramps!
[TRUNKS] After all!
She is your granddaughter!
[GOKU] Pan! You little rascal!
What a great performance! Wow!
Thanks!
Hi there, I guess we're
up next! My name's Goku!
Let's do our best!
Yeah sure! I'm looking
forward to it, Goku!
[ANNOUNCER] And now
it's time for the next bout!
Featuring Goku
and the youngster, Uub!
Goku has appeared in numerous
tournaments over the years
and is a former
World Champion himself!
He is a truly
remarkable fighter!
In my opinion,
he is second to none
among the competition here
and if I may make a prediction!
I think that it
will be Goku and Buu
fighting it out to see
who goes to the Championship!
Goku's opponent comes
from a small village
on a far away island!
He's the oldest
of five children!
His name is Uub and
he entered the tournament
in the hopes of
winning the prize money
so he can use it to buy
food for his village! Aww...
Give that boy a hot dog!
Two hot dogs! He needs
some meat on his bones!
[BULMA] It's a shame that
that nice boy traveled so far
only to get matched up
with Goku in the finals!
This is going to be the
true championship bout!
That's for sure!
[ANNOUNCER]
Fighters! Let the match begin!
Hey, don't be so tense!
You can't fight to your
full potential like that!
Yeah! Right!
He's so nervous!
[GOKU thinking]
He's got it bad!
I hate to do it, but this
calls for drastic measures!
Hey, kid! Your diaper's dirty!
I smell it from here!
Huh?
Oh, and drop the goody-goody
act, you stinky village rat.
And I'm gonna finish
that haircut for ya,
you half-pint
beauty school reject.
And, uhh... Oh, yeah!
You're plain ugly, too!
Yeah that's it!
And that's not surprising
when you consider what the
rest of your family looks like!
Is it? Ah, Mohawk boy!
[UUB thinking]
M-My family?
[GOKU] Your mother's so fat,
that cows moo at her!
[UUB]
How dare you insult my mother!
Huh?
Well, come on then, kid!
Right here! Right on my Uub!
What's your dad's deal?
I've never seen him
act like this before!
Yeah...
[GOKU thinking]
Now I'll go for the jugular!
Your dad's a bed wetter!
My mom isn't fat!
My family isn't ugly!
And my father's
not a bed wetter!
[NARRATOR]
Young Uub has finally snapped!
The dormant power
of the reborn Majin
is erupting in a fury.
The second round, which Goku
promised Buu ten years ago,
is about to get underway!