[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Trunks and Goten completed
their fusion training!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Fu... sion... Ha!
Yes! You're doing it!
Stay with it!
Whoa! It worked!
[NARRATOR] With their powers
successfully combined,
the fused warrior
Gotenks was born
and against better judgment,
he hastily set out to
do battle with Majin Buu.
[GOTENKS grunts]
[NARRATOR] Even with
all of Gotenks' strength,
the monster proved
much too resilient
for the young
fighter to handle.
[BUU screeches]
[NARRATOR] And he was forced
to return to his friends
at the Lookout...
[BULMA]
Did you beat Majin Buu?!
[NARRATOR]
...defeated.
[GOTENKS]
Not exactly...
He's a-a little
tougher than I thought!
[ALL groan]
[NARRATOR] Gotenks wasn't
the only one surprised
by Majin Buu's power.
The world's remaining
military forces
assembled in a desperate bid
to bring the monster down,
but to no avail.
Armed with their
mightiest weapons,
their efforts served only to
irritate the pudgy pink terror.
[GOTENKS] No! Run!
He's going to attack!
[BUU screams]
[NARRATOR]
With every passing hour,
humanity's hopes for survival
are growing
fainter and fainter.
Is there no one left
who can stand up
to the destructive
force of Majin Buu?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball Z!
[BUU]
Whoo-hoo! Buu go bang, bang!
Buu!
[PEOPLE scream]
[BUU]
Turn into candy!
[GIRL]
Ooh!
[PEOPLE scream]
[BUU]
Save for later.
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu continued
his destructive spree,
devouring untold scores of the
world's unsuspecting citizens.
The few remaining military
forces made a bid
to stop the monster
but were unable to withstand
Buu's awesome power.
Now, those few that remain
have gone into hiding,
hoping against hope that
a new hero will emerge.
[RADIO ANNOUNCER] Keep in mind
that the information we have
is pieced together from various
pirate radio broadcasts
around the world.
The devastation
seems to be non-ending,
with at a rough count,
only one fifth of the world's
population remaining.
All of our major
cities are gone.
The governments are
mostly destroyed
with any and all workable armies
completely out of commission.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is horrible.
However, we have heard
unsubstantiated rumors
that there may be someone left.
Someone left in this
world willing to fight.
I repeat, all
of this information
is unconfirmded at this time,
but as the news
trickles down to us
we will pass it along
to you immediately.
[RADIO ANNOUNCER B]
Interesting news here.
Hope for defeating
Majin Buu remains!
What we are beginning to
understand is that Mr. Satan
has been safely training
in his underground bunker,
protected by armed
guards at all times
from any type of outside threat.
Oh, this is amazing,
he is expected to
emerge sometime today!
The man who defeated Cell
is going to step up once again
as the savior for his planet!
[LIEUTENANT]
Atten-hut!
[cheering]
[CROWD chanting] Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
[cheering]
Yeaaaah!
[CROWD] Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
Your worrying days
are over, friend.
I'll take care of
this Buu clown for you.
Yes. I believe you will, sir.
[thinking]
Listen to them out there.
All they needed to give 'em
a little hope was a hero.
And now they got the
Champ--Mr. Satan!
[TRUNKS screams]
I can't stand that!
It's burning.
Well, if you don't stay still,
I'll never be able to clean it.
Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh!
[cries]
What did I do?
Stop it! You know exactly
what you did! Ten!
I'm sorry, but you're the only
thing I have left in this world.
The next time you want to go out
and do something so reckless,
try and remember that, okay?
'Kay, Mom...
Did you hear what she said?
Uh, yeah...
[PICCOLO] You both should
listen to your mothers.
No fighter that has
ever won a victory
did so using his fists alone.
All battles are won before
they are even fought,
and do you know how?
By planning?
That's right.
So you're saying that my dad
just didn't plan enough.
Then I run off
and do the same thing!
That's the last time,
from now on I'm doing it right.
I have to be smart to win,
a smarter fighter
than my dad ever was!
That's my Trunks...
[gasps]
You are both amazing young men.
Through each of your bodies
flows the blood of a warrior
who brought truth
to impossibility.
You two... will do the same.
[BOTH gasp]
[PICCOLO] None of this
will happen without
all of your efforts.
I suggest we begin immediately.
All right!
Good luck, honey!
Do your best, Goten.
Stay strong!
[MR. SATAN] So that's where
this bad boy lives, huh?
Uh, yes, that's what we've
been told, Mr Satan.
Well, you guys can relax now.
The Champ is on the scene.
And I'm gonna teach Majin Buu
not to mess with my fans!
[GENERAL] Oh, thank you, sir!
You are a true hero!
So brave and full of optimism.
Uh, excuse me, sir,
but what's in the bag?
Oh, it's nothing really,
just some toys.
Top secret toys
that'll make Majin Buu
wish he was never born!
Oh, top secret toys.
Can I take a look at them?
I have to save them for
when it counts, General.
I was told a long time ago
that the most
important key to victory
is the element of surprise.
And with what the surprises I've
got in store for this lowlife,
he's going to wish he never
heard the name Mr. Satan!
[growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[thinking]
Hmph. I am good.
[MR. SATAN]
You!
[BOTH gasp]
Yeah! You, Majin Buu!
It's time for you
to meet your maker!
[MR. SATAN] That's right!
Mr. Satan's here!
And you're gonna find
out what it's like
to have my boot
planted up your backside!
Now get out here,
you slime ball,
or I'm comin' in after ya...
[whispering] Either way,
you're going down.
[laughs quietly]
[GERNERAL]
Uh, Pardon me, Mr. Satan.
Please excuse my intrusion
but there seems to be something
wrong with your voice.
I've been fighting
a bit of a cold.
No problem!
It would be my pleasure
to help you in
your time of need.
Majin Buu, you worthless
piece of gutter trash,
get out here now!
[MR. SATAN]
Quiet!
[GENERAL squeals]
[MR. SATAN]
You keep shouting like that,
and someone's gonna hear you!
Phew...
I guess he hasn't
noticed us yet.
Look, this is my fight.
You two get out of here and
leave me to my concentration.
[GENERAL]
Yes sir, anything to help, sir.
The whole world owes you an
incredible debt of gratitude!
[MR. SATAN] Yeah, yeah.
Now you just hang out over there
by the plane or something.
And I'll call you
if I need anything.
[gasps]
Cowards. Well, at least
they're out of the way.
I sure hope Buu didn't
hear 'em taking off.
[MR. SATAN]
Be a tree... Be the tree...
[grunts]
[MR. SATAN]
Is... anybody home?
He's gone.
[laughs]
[grunts]
It looks like I'm all alone!
So, Mr. Big Pink Fatso,
I guess you got scared
and ran off, didn't you?!
Can't say I blame ya,
I'd be scared of me, too!
[laughs]
Here! I got somethin'
for ya! Take that!
[laughs]
[grass rustles,
gasps]
Oh, please, Mr. Buu sir!
I am so sorry! Really!
I-It was a mistake!
I would never do
anything to offend you
or this lovely home you've made!
[LIZARD beeps]
Ahh! Stu-pid Li-zard!
Who's scary now, huh?!
Don't sneak up
on me like that, again!
[BUU]
Helloooo!
Hey, you!
[gasps]
Oh, finally!
Mr. Majin Buu,
it's so good to see you!
I've been wanting to meet you
since I heard the first reports
of your worldwide devastation!
So... Do you want to
be candy, cookie, or pudding
when Buu eats you?
Wait, wait, wait!
I didn't come here to get eaten!
I-I came to bring
you some presents!
The best chocolates
money can buy!
Buu like big chocolates.
Eat you instead.
But these are packed
with the same amount
of chocolate-y goodness,
they're just made smaller
so you can eat a lot more.
They look good.
You want to eat, too?
Uh, no thanks,
I'm allergic to chocolate,
I break out in hives all over.
[sniffs]
[whimpers]
[thinking]
He ate it! I can't believe it!
Each one of those chocolates
has enough cyanide in it
to kill a water buffalo!
[gasps]
[BUU] Buu like! Better than
chocolate made from people!
[MR. SATAN]
I have something else.
Let's see... Oh, here it is.
A-A video game!
[MAJIN BUU]
Video game?
[MR. SATAN] See, you just use
the little buttons at the bottom
to control the guys
and punch and kick.
[GAME]
You win.
[laughs]
[GAME]
Game Over.
Video game cheat!
[screams]
Oh, I-I'm sorry about that!
I'm sure I can find a game
in here that doesn't cheat!
[thinking] Time to introduce Mr.
Buu to Mr. Plastic Explosive.
[chuckles]
Bye.
[MR. SATAN] Oh yeah!
I've just got two words to say!
The end!
Buu really like when the
video game goes boom!
[BUU giggles]
Wow, that's the part
most people would hate.
Buu think you should be
my new play friend.
That, uh, sounds great to me.
I'm not busy or anything.
This candy made
from people good.
[gasps]
Try some, you eat.
Oh, of course.
Human candy is some of my
favorite stuff in the world!
Oh, yeah, this candy is great.
It's sweet without
being too sweet,
kinda reminds me of the candy my
mom made me when I was a kid.
[MR. SATAN]
What's that?
What's what?
[MR. SATAN]
Huh? Huuh?
[BUU]
Huh...?
[growls, grunts]
[BUU]
What do you see?
I, uh, thought I saw a rabid
wolf or a poisonous rabbit
or something like that.
Buu make dead.
[BUU laughs]
[MR. SATAN] That was great.
Really, a magnificent shot.
Whatever that was over there,
you sure showed it who was boss!
I wouldn't want
to mess with you!
Uh, we're starting
to become friends,
so I think we should
preserve our new friendship
with, uh, some pictures!
[MR. SATAN] If you wouldn't
mind, lay down on belly
with your hands
out in front of you.
Like this?
[MR. SATAN]
I know it seems strange,
but this is the latest
style of picture taken.
Haah!
[chuckles]
[thinking]
There's one for the front page.
Say, Mr. Buu,
are you hungry at all?
I don't mean to brag,
but I'm a pretty good cook.
What d'ya say, hm?
[OLD KAI warbles]
[yawns]
[SUPREME KAI]
It's almost been five hours.
[OLD KAI warbles]
[warbling continues]
[sighs]
[OLD KAI warbles]
[chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[OLD KAI sighs]
Goku, I believe he's finished.
Was I asleep?
Oh sorry, I guess I
got a little bored there.
Boy, I'm exhausted,
I haven't done that in years.
[GOHAN grunts]
We can't thank you enough
for your hard work.
So, Gohan, you feeling any
of your new strength yet?
[OLD KAI] The ritual ended
less than a minute ago, sonny.
We've got 20 hours
before he'll feel anything.
[groans]
All righty, then.
Now you just have to sit here
and keep your mind's eye focused
on all of your energies,
never leaving this
meditative state.
I can't move at all?
[OLD KAI]
That's what it's going to take!
Discipline and concentration.
Only then can you
acquire what you seek.
Are you saying
it's not worth it?
Huh?
[GOKU laughs]
[GOHAN]
It's worth it...
Then get started.
No time like the present.
Whatever you say.
Ragh!
[NARRATOR] Now that Gohan
has entered the final stages
of the training ceremony,
his power will soon be increased
enough to combat Majin Buu.
But back on Earth,
how long will Mr. Satan
be able to hold
Buu's temper at bay?
[MR. SATAN] No, no,
allow me to wash your back.
Oh, it's my pleasure!
[thinking] Yeah, you just
enjoy your bath, tubby.
I've got you right
where I want you.
I hope.