[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta and Goku were
searching Majin Buu's head
for Gohan and the others.
[VEGETA] Okay, use your
instincts, Kakarot.
Right or left?
[GOKU]
Hmm? I'd have to say... Left.
[VEGETA]
Good. Then I'm going right.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU]
That's not very nice.
[GOKU] You follow
your instincts, Kakarot.
I'll follow mine.
Fine. Have it your way.
[NARRATOR] At last, good fortune
seemed to be smiling,
but Gohan wasn't.
Had Goku really found
his long lost son?
No. It was an imposter.
[GOKU] I can tell by
looking into your eyes
that you're not my son.
[NARRATOR] Vegeta was
battling equally dangerous
thought creations.
One had assumed
the form of Piccolo
in this funhouse of evil.
[VEGETA grunts]
Fool.
[NARRATOR] The other had taken
on the familiar form of Gotenks
to carry out Buu's
twisted purpose.
[GOTENKS grunts]
[VEGETA] Fighting both of those
idiots at once is pretty tough.
Where is that idiot
clown when you need him?
[NARRATOR]
But even with Goku's help,
the duo had no chance
against an enemy
that couldn't be destroyed.
[GOKU yelps]
[NARRATOR]
But lo and behold.
When Buu's concentration
shifted to sweets,
so did his thought forms.
And precious time was gained
to resume the search
for their sons and Piccolo.
[GOKU]
Now where could they have gone?
Over here. Take a look.
[NARRATOR]
Could it be?
Did Goku and Vegeta
find their boys at last?
[GOKU]
Hey.
Trunks and Goten have separated.
The Fusion Technique
must not work in here either.
No, not necessarily.
It could be just that their
fusion time has expired.
[VEGETA] Yes. Buu's thought
forms did perform the Fusion.
Perhap's you're right.
I hope so.
We're going to need every
advantage that we can get.
[chuckles]
[MR. SATAN]
Aiyee! Careful!
[SUPER BUU]
Mmm. Yum-yums...
[whimpers, laughs]
Hey. W-What's the deal?
Why are we sinking?
Would you back off?!
I'm not a super-hero!
[glass shatters]
[growls]
{BEE whimpers]
Twenty-five cake shops
down the hatch. Now.
[yelps]
[SUPER BUU laughs]
We're hitting some turbulence.
[DENDE]
It's not turbulence.
If it's not
turbulence, w-what is it?
Engine failure.
[sighs]
[MR. SATAN yells,
BEE yelps]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[DENDE]
I'm so sorry! Are you okay?!
Luckily, I landed on my head.
[whimpers]
This explosion will
light up all of space.
And planet Earth
will disappear forever.
[GOKU]
These things are weird.
They're squishy.
[GOKU]
It's kind of like an eggplant.
[VEGETA] Stand aside, Kakarot.
It's harvest time.
[GOKU yells, grunts]
[VEGETA] Or, maybe instead
of sitting around,
you can help me out.
[SUPER BUU whimpers]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[SUPER BUU grunts, yells]
My body.
What have they done?
Fools. I'll kill them!
[OLD KAI]
Woo-hoo! [laughs]
[KIBITO KAI]
Yes!
[BOTH laugh]
[OLD KAI]
It worked! It worked!
[KIBITO KAI]
Yes-yes-yes!
[laughing continues]
[BOTH retch, cough]
[BOTH laugh]
[GOKU]
Oh, yeah. Feel that?
Majin Buu's
changed back, all right.
What a difference!
[VEGETA]
Most definitely.
What a decrease. I like
the odds a lot better now.
Yes. Now let's blast
our way out of here.
Right.
Wait. Hold on just a second.
Even though he's a lot weaker,
we're still no match for him.
If we go out there right now,
he's going to kill us.
It's a problem, all right...
But there's one way we can win!
You can forget it,
Kakarot. No way.
I haven't even said what
it is yet, spoiled sport.
There's no need.
It begins with an F and
ends with an N. Am I right?
[GOKU]
Hey. Good guess.
[GOKU hums excitedly]
Come on. It only
lasts for 30 minutes
and then it's all over.
See? Huh-huh? Huh?
No way.
But it's only temporary.
That pose is not fit for a
Saiyan Warrior. It's too prissy.
What? Is that all?
What do you mean,
"Is that all"?!
That's enough! Where's your
dignity?! We're Saiyans!
Hmm? But no one's
going to see us.
Gosh, Vegeta.
Is it really that bad?
[growls]
We're fighters, not
ballet dancers, you oaf!
[growls]
Huh? Kakarot.
Look. You're not
going to believe this.
Huh? Majin Buu!
In his original form...
[VEGETA] Yes. I see that.
But what does it mean?
Who knows? How could he absorb
himself? Doesn't make sense.
Wow. This is deep.
Two Buus. Strange.
Maybe there were two Buus at
one time and this one lost.
[VEGETA]
You can't be serious?
[OLD KAI]
Uh-oh. Dadgum thing! Junk!
That's what it is!
They just don't make
'em like they used to!
But, Sir! I created
that one myself!
We could try to read
his mind. How 'bout it?
[VEGETA]
Hmm. I don't see why not.
Unless there's some kind
of strange energy block
like there was
with the earrings.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[GOKU] I guess there's
only one way to find out.
[VEGETA] Well, I suppose so.
Let's give it a go.
Go now!
[BUU whimpers]
Buu make you chocolate!
[BUU gasps, screams]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[MR. SATAN]
B-B-Buu a-ate Buu!
Wow. So there really
were two Majin Buus.
A nice one and a mean one.
Huh...
[VEGETA]
And old ugly won the battle.
[SUPER BUU] Who are you calling
"ugly," you ridiculous fool?
[GOKU]
Uh-oh.
[VEGETA] How can he be
inside of his own body?!
The real question is:
Why haven't you
two been absorbed yet?
And how dare you tamper
with my people pods?!
[SUPER BUU snarls]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot!
I think we're in trouble.
Well, why did you have
to crush your earring?!
You could've stuck
it in your pocket,
but no! You had to fix it
so we can never fuse again!
Thank you very much.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
I see. So you can't
join bodies anymore.
[VEGETA]
Nice work.
Is there anything else
you'd like to tell him?
[SUPER BUU]
Idiots. You're mine!
[SUPER BUU grunts, laughs]
[BOTH grunt]
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
I think I know how to get
that smirk off your ugly mug.
I'm gonna renovate your face.
[laughs]
Funny, huh? All right, then.
Allow me to add a skylight.
Go ahead. Try it.
If you insist.
[GOKU yells]
[SUPER BUU laughs]
What? No hole? Nothing?!
Yes. That's not good.
I felt it. It was
like a mosquito bite.
But for an
miniature guy like you
who's actually
smaller than a flea...
...that's... not so bad.
[GOKU] All right, then. We'll
escape and regain our size.
[GOKU grunts]
Getting by you shouldn't
be that difficult.
[yawns]
Oh really?
I don't know about that.
What d'ya say? Shall we?
Ready when you are.
[yawns]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunt]
[grunting]
[SUPER BUU] Oh, how scary.
A vicious attack.
[yawns]
[MR. SATAN]
Too bad. I guess we lost him.
[DENDE]
No, I can sense his spirit.
He's actually very close.
[gasps]
Wha-What do you mean,
you sense him?
That's right. Majin Buu's
energy signal, I can feel it.
What? Can I learn, too?
To sense things?
[DENDE] Sure. But you have to
relax and calm the mind.
I usually close my eyes.
[whimpers]
--[MR. SATAN] Tr-Tr-Tr-Tr-Tree!
--[DENDE gasps]
[yelling,
BEE squeals]
[DENDE]
What in the world is he doing?
He's like a statue.
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
He looks different.
What's the deal?
[gasps] You're right!
That's his previous form.
He's not as strong now.
[OLD KAI]
Gah! This darn thing!
[KIBITO KAI] Ah, Sir! We're
missing the most critical part!
[OLD KAI sighs]
I know!
[OLD KAI whines]
Peek-a-boo!
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[VEGETA]
I see you!
[VEGETA growls,
SUPER BUU grunts]
Huh?!
What?! He's getting away!
[VEGETA yelps]
[GOKU, VEGETA yell]
What's your head made of?!
Well, one pop
and they're both down.
That's using your heads, boys.
Vegeta. Let's shut him up.
[GOKU yells]
When I say "now", fire.
When I say "now", fire!
[VEGETA]
Now!
[BOTH yell]
[SUPER BUU screams]
I think that did the trick.
Now, if you don't mind,
I think I'd like to sit out
the rest of this dance.
Yeah, sure!
It looks like we have some
house cleaning to do anyway.
Ugh. Saiyans cheek-to-cheek
in battle. What's next?
[VEGETA groans]
Hey. We make
a good team, y'know?
Stay back! No more!
--Hmm?!
--What's that?!
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[SUPER BUU]
Aren't you forgetting something?
[GOKU]
What do you mean?!
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[SUPER BUU] Oh, good,
I've been looking for a chance
to use this.
Knock, knock.
KNOCK, KNOCK!
[VEGETA]
Who's there?
[SUPER BUU]
Buu.
Buu who?
[SUPER BUU] Aw. Don't cry.
Everyone has to die sometime.
[SUPER BUU laughs maniacally]
[SUPER BUU chuckles, laughs]
You just don't get it, do you?!
[yells]
[SUPER BUU] You can't
destroy me in this place!
It's Buu.
All Buu. Buu. Buu. Buu!
[laughs]
Take that, motor mouth!
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[VEGETA thinking]
How can I get him to shut up?!
He's driving me crazy!
[laughter continues]
[growls]
I can't... take it!
[yelling]
[laughing]
[gasps]
[GOKU]
The pods!
[VEGETA yells]
Hey. Easy there.
He's doing it on purpose.
We can't let him get to us.
We've got to keep our cool.
It's the only way we're
going to be able to beat him.
[VEGETA] You're right, Kakarot.
A warrior must remain detached.
[SUPER BUU]
Tick-tock. Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
Oh, don't be mad!
This isn't that bad of
a place to spend eternity.
You're time is running out!
[GOKU thinking] We'll see
whose time is running out.
Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
[GOKU yells]
[VEGETA] Kakarot,
you did it! Look, daylight!
That's our ticket out of here!
[SUPER BUU shrieks]
[gasps]
Enough! Our little game is over!
Now you become part of me!
[growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[SUPER BUU yells]
[GOKU, VEGETA scream]
[laughs]
[GOKU grunts]
[laughing continues]
[VEGETA grunts]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[NARRATOR] As Vegeta is
encompassed by the gushy,
slithering tissue,
it seems certain that
he will soon be a part
of the madman Majin Buu.
No!
[NARRATOR] Stay tuned for scenes
from the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!