[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z!
The tables were turned
on the demon king Dabura.
With the monster Majin
Buu at his bidding,
Babidi no longer had need
for his former right-hand man.
And the evil wizard was most
eager to see his new pet
cause some
delicious destruction!
Me eat you up! Me eat you up!
[NARRATOR] Quick to recognize
Buu's awesome potential,
Dabura was determined
to put a stop
to the seemingly
simple-minded creature
before he became too powerful
for Babidi to control.
[laughs]
Aaaaarrgh!!
[NARRATOR] But even
his mightiest efforts proved
to be in vain.
Me eat you up! Me eat you up!
Ah ha ha!
You turn into a cookie!
[NARRATOR] A flick of
Majin Buu's pink antenna
revealed one of the monster's
most uncanny abilities.
In an electrifying
display of power,
Dabura was reduced to
a harmless foodstuff.
[NARRATOR] And Buu
made good on his promise
to devour the King
of the Demon World.
[NARRATOR] Once again, Majin Buu
enjoyed the taste of victory.
But his delight
would not last long.
In a fiery blast that
sent Babidi reeling,
another fighter arrived
on the battlefield,
ready to challenge
the bloated beast.
[NARRATOR]
When the smoke cleared,
the wizard was shocked to
find his spaceship in ruins,
and the man responsible--Vegeta!
Hmph! Yes!
[NARRATOR] For what this
terrifying creature has done
to Gohan and the others,
Vegeta has sworn revenge!
And with Babidi's
magic augmenting
his already incredible
Super Saiyan strength,
it seems nothing will
stop him from having it!
[GOKU grunts]
Ve... Vege... ta...
No! Majin Buu? What's going
on? He's beating you?!
Why can't you do to him
what you did to the others?!
[VEGETA] Is this the best
your monster can do, Babidi?
The "terror of the universe"?
Hah! Pathetic.
Uh, wow. And here I thought
he couldn't get any cockier.
Haha haha haha.
[TRUNKS]
Yeah!
All right! Go for it, Dad!
You can do it!
You got him right where you
want him, now finish him off!
Haha! Yeah go get him!
[PICCOLO thinking]
Something's happened to Vegeta.
Even for a Super Saiyan,
he seems unnaturally strong!
[gasps]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[PICCOLO thinking] Amazing!
His energy, it's enormous!
I haven't sensed
anything like this since..
since Gohan fought Cell!
But Majin Buu was
able to take Gohan down.
He killed him! I only hope
Vegeta can avoid the same fate.
He's the last chance we've got.
And if he fails. No!
Vegeta, you can't fail!
Unless Goku reappears,
all of our lives--this whole
world--depends on you!
[BUU]
Hmm?
Majin Buu!
Don't let him do this to you.
Just eat him or
squash him or something.
Oh... Uh...
Whoa...
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
I knew my dad could beat him!
All right! Goten!
Victory is ours! Heh!
Trunks! Your dad's the best!
Well, of course! I guess you
could say it runs in the family!
[GOTEN laughs]
[BUU]
Oof!
Huh?!
Aahhh! Ooo!
Heehee!
[BUU grunts]
What the...?
[cackles loudly]
Buu! You are positively
wonderful! I love you!
Now go and destroy him!
[BUU hums]
[BABIDI]
Buu, what are you waiting for?
Finish him!
Tear him to ribbons!
Do you hear me? Ribbons!
I don't want there to
be anything left of him
when you're through!
Show him what happens to people
who blow up my spaceship!
[BABIDI]
Are you even listening to me?
I'm giving you an order!
Do something!
Do you want me to put
you back in your ball?
Because I wil!!
If he's not die by the
time I count to three...
One, two...
Get him, Dad!
[BABIDI]
Three!
[screams]
Aaah!
Oh...
Yeah!
Hoo-ray! Hoo-ray! Hoo-ray!
He did it! All right!
[snickers]
[BABIDI]
No.. No.. How could this happen?
My pet is gone...
My beautiful pet is gone! Ah!
Huh?!
Yay, Dad! Hahaha!
Huh?
[grunts]
[snickers] No, no!
Buu no drop dead.
What is he? Immortal?
[BABIDI]
Oh ho, yes, victory! Hahahaha!
Go Majin Buu! Pow! Pow!
Pow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Isn't that right, Buu!
"Drop him dead!"
or whatever it is you say.
Big power.
[KRILLIN] Uh, guys, this
looks like our cue to leave.
[TRUNKS] But, we can't!
We can't just leave my dad!
[KRILLIN] I think your dad
knows how to handle himself!
Whadda ya say we get outta here!
Wait... What is this?
Me mad now!
Me get big... MAD!!
Ah? Barrier!
Everyone! Take cover!
[pants]
Incredible.
Is everyone all right?
Oh yeah... Feel great!
Ow ow ow...
Hey! Uh, has anybody
seen Goten around?
[laughs]
[TRUNKS laughs]
Kid, don't scare me like that!
Bye! See ya later, Mr. Lizard.
No! Vegeta, can you hear me?!
Father!
[VEGETA groans]
Bububuuu! Bububuu!
Bububuuu!
Ohh! Hohoho! Haaaa!
Curse that thing!
How can I beat him if he's
able to regenerate himself
after every attack? Darn him!
That fool thought he was so
tough but just look at him now.
He's nothing compared to you
Majin Buu! He's nothing at all!
Too bad he had to go
and disobey me.
He would have made
such a fine subordinate!
Father...
[PICCOLO] I don't think
even Vegeta will be able
to do this on his own.
And Gohan, Goku, the Supreme
Kai, all of them are gone!
If Majin Buu wins now.. there
will be no one left to stop him.
Hold on! My dad is
way too strong to lose
to that creep right, Piccolo?
Piccolo?
[BUU]
Uh-oh!
You no fun.
You go bye bye! Bye bye!
Bye bye! Bye bye! Bye bye!
[VEGETA thinking] I have to try
harder. He must have a weakness!
If this thing can be given life,
he can also have it taken away!
[gasps]
[KRILLIN]
Euggh! Eww!
Oooooohhhh!
Ugh! What a disgusting
creature. What is he up to now?
Oh, come on!
[BUU hums]
Huh?!
So! Are you going to fight me,
or are you just going to spit?
Aaaaaaaaa!
What?!
[snickers]
Ah!
Buu-hoohoo!
[VEGETA grunts]
[BUU hums]
Oh no!
Hahaha!
Augh!!
[laughs]
[KRILLIN]
Vegeta's a goner!
Man I wish Goku
and Gohan were here!
Where the heck are
those guys anyway?
Hey! They'll be here,
Krillin! Just wait!
[PICCOLO]
Stay where you are Trunks!
We don't want to lose you too!
There's nothing you can do now!
You'll just cause Vegeta
more pain if you get involved!
[laughs]
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
Hyaaaa!!
Trunks wait up!
[BUU]
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
Ha!!
[NARRATOR]
To Babidi's great amusement,
Vegeta is getting the beating
of his life from Majin Buu.
The Saiyan Prince is strong,
but unable to defend himself
how much of this
pounding can he withstand?
[BUU laughs]
[NARRATOR] Can the two young
Super Saiyans, Trunks and Goten,
save Vegeta
before it's too late?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!