[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
his patience at an end,
Frieza prepared to finish off
the Z Fighters once and for all.
As Vegeta and the others
looked on in horror,
the evil tyrant at last revealed
the true depths of his power.
With a mighty roar,
Frieza summoned his energy
and began a monstrous
transformation.
His body bulged and strained
as the tyrant unleashed the
sleeping terror within,
and as his size swelled
to enormous new proportions,
so did his strength and speed.
Having taken this hideous shape,
Frieza's already nightmarish
powers were increased tenfold.
[NARRATOR] At last, his
transformation complete,
Frieza set his sights on
the Z Fighters once more.
Well, this is it. I hope
you're not disappointed.
[NARRATOR] Gohan, Krillin,
and Vegeta gaped in awe
at the monster before them,
but little did they know,
the real horror
was still to come.
As Frieza settled
into his new body,
he prepared to demonstrate
his might by eliminating
the Z Fighters one by one.
[FRIEZA roars]
Huh?! What?!
[KRILLIN screams]
Krillin!
[NARRATOR] Helpless
to defend himself,
Krillin has become the
first of Frieza's targets.
Impaled on the monster's horns,
the hero's demise
now seems certain.
Can Gohan save his friend
before it's too late?
Or is this but a taste of what's
in store for all of our heroes?
Find out today on Dragon Ball Z!
[GOHAN] No! Krillin!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Ugh. What an idiot.
He should have never
tried to stand up
for that insignificant
Namekian kid.
[DENDE whimpers]
I tried to tell him,
but he wouldn't listen.
Now it looks like
it's over for him.
[KRILLIN groans]
[FRIEZA] Oh, I'm sorry!
Does that hurt?
I guess I just don't
know my own strength.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[KRILLIN screaming]
[GOHAN] Frieza... you monster!
Oh, I beg of you, please
don't hurt little old me!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
I... can't breathe...
[KRILLIN grunts]
[GOHAN screams]
[KRILLIN shouting,
FRIEZA laughing]
Stay with it! Yee-haw! That's
it, buckaroo! Ride 'em, cowboy!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[KRILLIN screams]
[VEGETA growls]
[YAMCHA] Aw man, how long
do we have to be stuck up
here in this living--
Calm down, Yamcha.
Yeah, cool it already!
[YAMCHA] How do you
expect me to be calm?!
Gohan and Krillin are down
there fighting our battle,
while we're stuck up
here just watching
and waiting for them to
defeat that stupid Frieza!
And there isn't...
anything I can do to help.
[YAMCHA] Calm down!
Yeah right!
I'm just as frustrated
as you are!
But getting mad isn't
going to solve anything!
Yeah, and I'm sure Goku and
Piccolo can get the job done!
Hey, just take it easy, okay?
You know we can't leave this
place until the battle is won.
So, in the meantime,
try and relax, alright?
Yeah!
[KING KAI] Goku, how
many times did I warn you
to stay clear of Frieza?
And now that his
powers have increased,
there may only be one
possibility that remains.
That we're all doomed!
[KING KAI whimpers]
[TIEN] King Kai?
Huh? Yes. Uh, what can I do for
you? How's your training going?
We were just wondering,
are you feeling okay?
Yeah, you look a little pale!
Yes. I think it just
might be a little gas.
We-We want to know what's
happening on Planet Namek!
[KING KAI growls]
Quit stalling!
[growling continues]
Is there something wrong?
[BULMA] I can't go on...
No, this can't be happening
to me! It's all a bad dream!
I haven't had a shower in days!
I wish... I was
a fluffy cloud...
Huh?
Ah, that looks
like Krillin!
[BULMA giggles]
Oh my!
Call me crazy, but I think
I'm starting to lose it!
This is not good!
[BULMA] Even worse,
what if Gohan and Krillin
have forgotten all about me
in this miserable wasteland?
Oh my, what if Vegeta or
Frieza did them in? Oh no!
That almost makes my bad
hair day seem insignificant!
That means I'll
never love again!
Mind you, that would
require a date!
You gettin' tired up
there big fella, huh?
[FRIEZA laughs]
[KRILLIN] I can't believe it...
Looks like this is the end...
Frieza's just too powerful...
Goku... Goku, where were you...?
[GOKU] Hang in there, Krillin!
Once these wounds have healed
I'll be there for you, buddy!
Be strong...
Hm, hm! That takes
care of this one.
Ah! Krillin!
[FRIEZA] Hmm!
How?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
You really think you can save
him? Sorry. It's too late.
Might I suggest you start
worrying about yourself, boy?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Now, who's going to be next?
Let's see. Will it be you?
[DENDE whimpers]
Or how about you?
[GOHAN growls]
It makes no difference to me!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOHAN] You...
...a-ni-maaaal!
[VEGETA gasps]
[GOHAN shouting]
[GOHAN shouts]
[GOHAN] Raagh!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOHAN shouts,
FRIEZA gasps]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN shouting]
[VEGETA] What's going on?
This kid seems to be getting...
...stronger!
[GOHAN yelling]
[GOHAN] Haaaahh...
[GOHAN growls]
[VEGETA] Look at his
power. And it's increasing!
[growling continues]
[GOHAN] Masenkooo...
Haaa!
[GOHAN growls]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN panting]
[VEGETA] I can't believe
it! I-It's impossible!
From out of nowhere he
just explodes with power
like I've never seen before!
What the--!
That's... That's impossible!
No! There's just no way that
kid could be a Super Saiyan!
It-It can't be!
[GOHAN pants]
Ahh...?
K-Krillin?
Ar-Are you there...?
K-Krillin!
[DENDE] He's okay, Gohan!
He's still breathing!
Ar... Are you sure...
he'll survive?
[VEGETA] We don't have time
to be worrying about him!
If you think you finished
off Frieza, just look!
Huh?!
Hey kid, I must admit
that you surprised me.
But don't let it
go to your head,
because after all, you're
nowhere near my equal!
Let's just say your
attacked rated a two
on a scale of
one to a zillion.
Now, I think it's time we get
this little skirmish over with!
[VEGETA] Why, you monster!
So, now what are we
supposed to do, Einstein?!
'Cause there's no way in
the world we can beat him!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[rumbling]
[GOHAN] Aah! Oh my gosh!
His power level, it's
getting even stronger!
[rumbling continues]
[VEGETA] You're right, kid!
And we're sitting ducks!
The pain that you
have caused me,
I will return it tenfold!
[DENDE grunts]
[DENDE screams]
[GOKU] Frieza's power
has risen again!
If I don't get
out there, and quick,
Gohan doesn't stand a chance!
[GOKU] Gohan!
Kid, no! Move! Look out!
[GOHAN grunts]
Come on. You can't tell me
that I won with just one hit!
Honestly, I was
expecting a little more!
[GOHAN grunts]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Well, it
wasn't much of a fight,
but it was fun while it lasted.
[VEGETA] Hey, Frieza!
[FRIEZA] Hmm...?
[explosion]
[VEGETA laughs]
Alright. Rule number one:
Never turn your back...
when you're up against Vegeta!
[VEGETA growls]
Because with me,
the battle is never over,
And there's a good chance
I've got a couple
tricks up my sleeve...
[VEGETA laughs]
Feel my wrath!
Raaaugh!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Never underestimate the
power of a true Super Saiyan!
So while you gloat about
how strong you are,
I'll be the victor!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA stutters]
Don't look so surprised, Vegeta.
[VEGETA gasps]
[FRIEZA] I'll be right with you,
but first, I must exterminate
the mighty midget!
[VEGETA] Oh, no. We're all
doomed. We're doomed!
Now then, would you like
to have another shot at me?
[GOHAN groans]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOHAN growls]
[shouting]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOHAN gasps]
Where'd he...
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN screams]
[FRIEZA] Sometimes you just
gotta put your foot down
when it comes to kids.
[GOHAN screams]
Bye-bye... Brat.
[skull cracking]
[PICCOLO] Hang in there,
Gohan! I'm on my way!
Just don't give up!
Please, don't give up!
[GOKU] Gohan...
[NARRATOR] Can Gohan survive
until help arrives?
Will Vegeta come to
our hero's aid?
Or is Gohan's fate at the mercy
of the relentless Frieza?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball Z!