[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
Piccolo took on the ruthless
Frieza in a one-on-one battle.
With Piccolo and Nail
becoming one,
it appeared the fight against
the all powerful Frieza
had finally turned around.
[NARRATOR] Was the Namek
pair strong enough?
At least for a while
it appeared so.
All we have to do
is fight as one.
[NARRATOR] As Frieza learned
of the Namekian trick,
he upped his efforts,
launching an incredible blast.
[NARRATOR] But the new
Piccolo reflected it,
sending it straight back
to the evil Frieza!
However, it would take more than
that to stop this villain.
[NARRATOR] Piccolo gathered
his strength for another
massive assault
against Frieza.
[FRIEZA screams]
What the...?
[NARRATOR] But when
the smoke cleared,
Frieza was still standing.
[NARRATOR] The battle
continues... today!
Oh, wow. It looks like Piccolo
whipped Frieza's butt!
No! It is not over with!
Hey, Vegeta, from what I've
seen, Frieza's finished!
[thinking] Oh, these morons
just don't get it!
There's no way that
Frieza's dead!
And they think this is easy...
All right! Thanks to Piccolo,
Frieza's finally bit the dust!
Right on!
[thinking] Now I see why Piccolo
wanted to merge with Nail.
Their combined power was just
too much for Frieza to handle!
[thinking] Frieza's power level
is way down! Come on, guys...
You gotta tell us...
Did Piccolo defeat Frieza,
or are we still stuck up here
in this eternal limbo?!
Let's put it this way,
he's our only hope.
[KING KAI] Hmmm...
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOHAN screams]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[PICCOLO] What the--?!
Ah! It doesn't matter how
quick I make a move,
he still beats me!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
What'd we do now...?
Don't worry, Gohan!
It's just like they say:
"It ain't over 'til
the fat lady sings!"
Well, I'd say she just
hummed a few bars.
[thinking] I've got to
find a way outta here.
I could save
myself at least...
[thinking] Nail...
[GOKU] Oh no! Piccolo!
What's happening?
Piccolo!
Well, King Kai?!
It is out of my hands.
All we can do right now
is trust in Piccolo.
[BOTH growl]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Well, it looks like
the tables have turned again,
my friend, and this
time for the last time!
So, are you ready for a
taste of your demise?
Because it's coming
up right now!
[thinking] Darn it,
Frieza's taken a beating
and he's still not down!
How did I ever think I
could beat him on my own?
[FRIEZA] Hmm...?
[bones popping]
Alright, Frieza.
I don't have all day.
What?! You're serious?
Hmph.
[FRIEZA] Well, I will give you
bonus points for courage.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] But that's all one
could expect from a Namek.
Sticks and stones, Frieza.
[thinking] Piccolo, you idiot!
Don't make him any angrier!
What the--? Piccolo!
I think I get it!
Piccolo's gathering up his
strength inside from Nail,
and then he's going to
turn it all on Frieza!
Huh...?
It's time you feel the wrath
of all the Nameks
you've destroyed!
[PICCOLO yells]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[thinking] I can feel Piccolo's
strength. It's growing!
And it's bigger
than it's ever been!
Piccolo! I know
you can beat him!
Go for it! Come on!
Perhaps I was wrong
about this one?!
[FRIEZA] Well, I don't know
about you, but I'm ready.
So, whenever you're
finished "powering up",
then maybe we can
get started, hmm?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[PICCOLO yells]
Huh?
[FRIEZA grunts]
Huh?!
[PICCOLO laughs]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laugh]
Oh, by the way, you
cow-headed clown,
I'm only getting warmed up.
[FRIEZA growls]
--[KRILLIN laughs]
--Yeah!
Did you see that?!
[DENDE laughs]
You did it, Nail!
I can't believe
it's over, Krillin.
Me neither.
[thinking] It looks like Piccolo
really did it this time.
And with Frieza out of the way,
it's only a matter of time until
I destroy the rest of them!
[VEGETA chuckles]
And for good measure!
[PICCOLO growls]
[ALL grunting]
[GOHAN] You think
Frieza's history?
[KRILLIN] I hope so!
It's over!
[ALL gasp]
What does a Namek have to do?
I just wish you could get
it through your head...
You can't defeat me!
Just watch me!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Your problem is you don't
know how strong I really am.
See, there is one thing
I should tell you about,
and that's my
power to transform.
You didn't see my
first transformation,
but I have others.
And each time, my strength
becomes much stronger.
Which means all your efforts
were against a weak me.
Understand?
Good! Now that that little
business has been cleared up,
I think it's about
time I finish you off!
[FRIEZA] Now you'll
see I wasn't bluffing
because I'll be transforming
before your very eyes.
Watch carefully now.
And keep in mind it's
not my ultimate form.
I still have one more
transformation!
You're full of it.
What's he doing?
Well, I'd say...
he's in trouble!
Y-You're right. Especially
if Frieza transforms again.
[thinking] You know, it's times
like this I think to myself:
Why didn't I just become
a shoe salesman?!
[FRIEZA] I suggest you stand
back while I demonstrate.
Ladies and gentlemen,
with great honor
I present to you
the most amazing
transformation ever witnessed!
[gasping]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Take a
good look, Namek.
'Cause after all, you'll
never live to see another.
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA groaning]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[groaning continues]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[DENDE whimpers]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] So, tell me,
how do I look?
I may not win any
beauty contests,
but I'll beat your tail!
You? Disgusting.
[FRIEZA laughs]
Well, it doesn't look like
Frieza changed that much.
Are you kidding?! Unless you've
completely lost it, baldy,
Frieza's probably
indestructible, now!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
I don't get it. How'd
Frieza recover so fast
after everything
Piccolo did to him?
[GOKU thinking] What's
going on out there?
I can sense Frieza's power
growing every second.
But if I don't get my
strength back pretty quick,
we don't stand a chance!
And if that happens, I could
never forgive myself.
[thinking] Frieza has
turned into a far greater
monster than I ever imagined!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[PICCOLO growls]
[FRIEZA} You seem
pretty sure of yourself,
so why don't you come
and get a piece of me?
Well, it looks like I'll have
to get the ball rolling again.
[FRIEZA] Ha-ha!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[thinking] You may be
stronger than me, Frieza,
but with my speed,
you'll never catch me!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[thinking] It's not possible!
Well, hello there.
Haven't we met before?
It's been so long
waiting for you.
Boy, it looks like Frieza's
way faster than Piccolo.
Faster, stronger, you name it!
Frieza's has Piccolo beat.
[thinking] C'mon, Nail,
hang in there!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Please listen. I have
the power to heal you.
[VEGETA thinking] Ah, yes,
the little green one.
He's going to come in handy.
[PICCOLO growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[YAMCHA thinking]
We believe in you, Piccolo.
[TIEN thinking]
Yes...
[PICCOLO grunts]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO yelling]
[FRIEZA yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[gasping]
[grunting]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Now, now, you're not
giving up already, eh?
[PICCOLO growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
So you really thought
your "superior speed"
was going to save you, eh?
Well, you're a lot
dumber than you look,
you inferior little Namekian.
Looks like it's time
to shut out the lights!
Haaah!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[groaning]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[PICCOLO grunting]
Ahhh! Piccolo!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[grunting continues]
Oh man, would ya look at that?!
How much more
can Piccolo take?
[PICCOLO grunting]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[thinking] Hang on, Piccolo...
[DENDE whimpers]
[grunting,
laughing]
[thinking]
What's happening, Piccolo?!
[GOHAN growls]
[growling continues]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN growls]
Gohan! Come back!
Gohan!
No, Krillin!
What do you think
you're doing, Vegeta?!
Come on, Krillin.
Don't be a fool!
[KRILLIN] But... Gohan
will never make it!
Look at me! if you really want
to save your little friend,
beat me up!
Don't waste your time taking on
Frieza. This is our only chance!
[thinking] If Krillin can beat
me to within an inch of my life,
that kid down there will heal me
and I'll finally become...
a true Super Saiyan!
[GOHAN yells]
[NARRATOR] Will Gohan arrive
in time to save Piccolo?
Or is Frieza too
powerful to defeat
since his second
transformation?
And how will Krillin handle
a battle with Vegeta?
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!