[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
our heroes' worst
fears were realized
when Cell absorbed Android 17
into his being.
Fueled by this union,
Cell underwent a mighty
transformation,
moving him one step closer to
his final terrifying form.
[CELL] Ahh, yes!
This is much nicer!
How exhilarating!
[NARRATOR] The reformed Cell
was certainly a sight to behold.
But what sort of
horrifying new power
accompanied this shocking
new appearance?
[CELL] Ah, a new look!
Much more comely than the last!
Merging with 18 should
have a similar effect.
[CELL] I can't wait!
[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
Bulging in his new body,
Cell was able to quickly
overcome the ox-like 16.
[ANDROID 18]
Look what you've done.
You're a monster!
[NARRATOR]
It seemed no one could stop Cell
from absorbing Android 18
and reaching his completion.
[CELL]
My dear android,
when will you understand
that you belong to me?
[NARRATOR]
Then, in a daredevil move,
Tien ambushed Cell
with a bold new attack!
But how long can he keep it up?!
Find out today
on Dragon Ball Z!
[CELL] When I get out of here
I will make you pay!
[CELL growls]
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN yells]
[CELL shouts]
[CELL grunting]
[grunting continues]
[TIEN yelling]
[TIEN] What are
you two waiting for?!
Get out of here now!
Hurry, before it's too late!
Go! Now!
Come on, 16!
This is our only chance!
Yes... We should...
[CELL grunting]
[TIEN yelling]
[CELL yelling]
[ANDROID 18] Come on, 16!
Come on! We have to go!
[CELL shouting]
[CELL growls]
No! They can't escape!
[CELL snarls]
[TIEN yells]
[CELL grunts]
Stop that!
Yeah! In your dreams!
[TIEN yells]
[CELL grunting]
[TIEN yelling]
Man! How long can
Tien keep fighting?
He's strong...
But Cell is stronger.
Tien will not be able
to last much longer.
His life force is slipping away.
He must stop.
Or, the next energy blast
he fires could be his last!
No! I won't let that happen!
All we need is some more time!
[GOKU growls]
It's up to me now.
I must stop Cell.
I can't give up! No!
[TIEN growls]
[CELL yells]
Is something wrong, Yamcha?
Yeah, I'm worried about Tien.
[CHIAOTZU] I'm worried
about him too, Yamcha.
[CHIAOTZU] He's in trouble.
Chiaotzu? You're back!
Please... Do something...
Please, save Tien...
[ROSHI] I'm sorry, Chiaotzu.
Tien is on his own right now.
We can't save him, even though
we want too. Believe me...
[CHICHI]
What are you talking about?
Shame on you!
You can't give up.
You know Goku would
never do a thing like that.
When he and Gohan
finish their training,
they're gonna bash
that monster good!
[YAMCHA] Yeah, right.
I guess it's not over yet...
I hope Tien can hang on.
He's alone.
Chiaotzu, let's go!
Yes! I'm ready!
[ROSHI]
Wait a minute!
I'm well aware that Tien
means a lot to both of you...
But if you get involved now,
you'll only become two
more of Cell's victims.
But...
[ROSHI]
No! Listen to me...
Do you think that I like
standing around here
doing nothing?
ChiChi is correct.
We need Goku's help!
You must stay here!
Rats!
Tien... stay alive...
Goku...
[TIEN yelling]
[CELL grunting]
[TIEN] These blasts are...
taking everything from me...
But I must go on...
Just a little longer...
[CELL growls]
[TIEN growls]
[yelling]
[CELL growls]
[CELL grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU gasps]
[YAMCHA gasps]
No! Tien!
[CELL] Curses! 18 has
managed to escape my sight!
[CELL] All because of
that insolent meddler!
[TIEN groans]
You puny man...
Now you realize
how pointless it is
to try to stop the inevitable.
[TIEN grunts]
Ah... Tien has given out.
[GOHAN growls]
Dad... We've got to help him!
I... know!
[GOKU growls]
[CELL] Hmmm...
Rrgh! I can't believe
such a weakling held me back!
[TIEN groans softly]
It's almost too
embarrassing to take.
I'll squash him!
[GOKU gasps]
Where'd... he go?
[CELL] Hmm?
It's Goku!
[GOKU] Why don't you back off
and leave my friend alone?
So you're Goku.
And I take it you're Cell.
Well, Goku, it's so
nice to meet you.
Yeah, I bet.
So you can add another head
over your mantle, right?
[CELL chuckles]
I'd really like to
teach you a lesson...
But I need one more day
before I'm strong enough
to go up against you.
And I'll make you pay, Cell!
Your days of terrorizing the
Earth will be finished for good!
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] Here I've always wondered
what it would be like
to face the legendary Goku.
And all you have to say
is "see you tomorrow"?
How disappointing.
From all I've heard,
I never would have
pegged you as a coward...
[thinking]
I sense Piccolo! He's alive!
Hold on, Piccolo!
I'll be there in just a second!
What?!
Hang in there. Everything's
going to be okay now, Tien.
Thanks, Goku...
Huh?
[CELL] Clever trick!
But they didn't get very far!
Piccolo!
Hey, Piccolo, are you okay?
Huh? What's this?
How could he still be living?
I was too careless...
Just hang in there, guys! I'll
take care of the both of you.
I'll get you some of
Korin's Senzu beans
the minute we get back
to Kami's place!
[TIEN groans]
No, Goku. We will
fight right now!
[GOKU gasps]
They disappeared?!
Where did they go this time?
That's quite a move! I must
find out how he does that!
Well, that will be the last time
that they will get away from me!
I'll deal with them soon,
but finding Android 18
is much more important
to me right now.
[GOHAN]
Piccolo!
[GOHAN] Are they okay, Dad?
Yes, Son, but they both
need a Senzu bean right away!
[GOHAN]
Okay!
Huh?
I wonder what that is...
Hey, it's Bulma!
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
What? What is it, Trunks?
Are you hungry?
Krill-oo! Krill-oo!
What? Krillin?
Where? I-I don't see him yet.
[KRILLIN laughing]
[BULMA gasps]
That's him alright!
Yay, Trunks! Good call!
What a smart boy you are!
You're a real genius,
just like your mom!
Okay. Should we see
what he wants, huh?
[KRILLIN]
Hey, Bulma!
Listen, I really need
that remote control
to stop those androids, okay?
[BULMA] Sure, Krillin.
But be careful.
I put a lot of work into it.
Wow. So this little
thing will stop them, huh?
Now you'll have to get within
10 meters of the androids
to be in range.
Any farther away
and it won't work.
Huh? Uh... 10 meters?
[KRILLIN gulps]
Gee, don't you think
that's kind of close?
Don't complain! You're lucky
you have that thing at all!
Uh... yeah, of course.
I'll try to keep that in mind.
[BULMA]
Well, you better!
[KRILLIN]
Hey, what have you got there?
I got everyone a combat
suit just like Vegeta's.
This one is for you.
It's very comfortable.
And of course, durable!
[KRILLIN] Thanks, Bulma,
We're gonna need those.
Hey, Goku, Gohan,
Trunks, and Vegeta
are training at Kami's
place right now.
Could you take
their suits to them?
[BULMA]
Kami's place?
Wow! That's above
Korin's Tower isn't it?
[KRILLIN] Yeah, that's right.
Think you can do it?
Okay! I'll go to Kami's.
But you take that remote
and shut down those
androids for good!
Sure thing.
[BULMA] Okay... Say "bye-bye"
to Krillin, little Trunks!
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
Adios, little guy.
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[KRILLIN thinking]
Guess it's in my hands now...
I hope this thing works.
[CELL growls]
So, they think they have
escaped me? They are mistaken.
[ANDROID 18] 17...
I can't believe you're gone...
I guess those Senzu beans
did the trick.
You look like you're
feeling a lot better.
You bet! And I thought
I was gone for good this time.
Next time, Tien, don't try
to do everything by yourself!
You had us all really
worried about you, Tien.
But that was really cool
how you stopped Cell
from absorbing
that other android!
I don't know if I
could have done that.
[PICCOLO] It was
an honorable move, Tien.
But let's remember:
it still wasn't enough!
It's going to take a force
much stronger than all of us
to defeat Cell now!
Think about it.
Not one of us...
can take that guy down.
Not even you, Goku...
We're going to need
something... more...
[MR. POPO]
Goku!
Huh?
Come quick!
Vegeta and Trunks are coming out
of the Hyperbolic Time Chamber!
'Bout time!
[MR. POPO]
I heard strange sounds
coming from inside the chamber.
I believe their time is up!
[NARRATOR] At long last,
the moment of truth has arrived!
After a year of unseen training,
Trunks and Vegeta have emerged
from the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber!
But do these hardened
Saiyans possess the strength
necessary to defeat
the most terrible villain
ever to threaten the Earth?
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next explosive episode
of Dragon Ball Z!