[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Frieza spoiled the
surprise when he noticed
Goku's secret weapon,
the Spirit Bomb!
[FRIEZA] But where did
he get so much power?!
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[NARRATOR] Of course,
Frieza wasn't about to
let Goku have the upper hand,
deciding to stop the Spirit
Bomb dead in its tracks.
And as Frieza
well knows,
the best way to
solve a problem
is to go directly
to the source!
Bad news for Goku!
[FRIEZA] Ka-boom.
[NARRATOR] But suddenly,
Piccolo came charging
to the rescue!
Piccolo?!
Goku...
You must hurry and finish
collecting energy for your bomb!
[FRIEZA growls]
[NARRATOR] Now, can Piccolo
keep Frieza busy long enough
for Goku to complete
his Spirit Bomb?
Stay tuned and find out!
[GOKU grunts]
[grunting continues]
[FRIEZA growls]
Where did he come from?!
I thought I rid myself of all
the Nameks a long time ago!
[GOHAN growls]
[PICCOLO] C'mon, Goku...
You've gotta hurry!
How long until your
Spirit Bomb is ready?!
It looks like Frieza's
about to attack again!
No...
Not yet...
I need a little
more time, Piccolo!
Aah!
Throw it Goku, throw it!
No! I can't!
It's not strong enough
to defeat him yet!
[PICCOLO growls]
Look what we have here.
The last, pathetic Namek.
Wanna piece of me?
Well, come and
get it, if you can.
Piccolo?
What's he
trying to do?
He can't win!
[GOHAN] What?!
He must be trying
to stall Frieza
while Goku powers up
the Spirit Bomb!
I've gotta a bad
feeling about this, Gohan!
As powerful as Frieza is,
Piccolo's just making
a death wish...
No, Piccolo!
[KRILLIN] Gohan, wait!
[GOHAN] Huh?!
Mm-mmm...
[GOHAN growls]
Goku... Please hurry...
[PICCOLO shouts]
Ouch. That almost tickled.
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO shouts]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[FRIEZA] Hmph.
[PICCOLO screams]
[FRIEZA giggles,
screaming continues]
You know, there's
nothing more annoying
than a screaming Namek.
[PICCOLO grunts]
There, see?
That's sounds better.
[PICCOLO] Goku...
I'm sorry...
I can't hold him off
any longer...
You've gotta do
something... soon...
[GOKU grunts]
[thinking] I'm trying, Piccolo!
[KING KAI] Oh no...
No, Piccolo!
[GINYU FORCE chuckles]
They're disgusting!
Yeah, but remember what
they did to Vegeta.
They may look stupid,
but these guys are tough.
Take that!
[ALL grunting]
[CHIAOTZU gasping]
[GULDO laughing]
[CHIAOTZU] Help!
Someone help me!
Yamcha! Tien!
He's gaining on me!
[CHIAOTZU grunts]
[KING KAI] Hmm...
You can't give up!
These goofs aren't that tough!
Bu-But King Kai!
It's three against four!
These guys are
awesome fighters!
King Kai! Give us a break here!
[RECOOME chuckles]
[RECOOME growls]
This doesn't look good!
[JEICE yells]
[JEICE screams]
[BURTER gasps]
What the heck...?
Hey, these morons aren't
as tough as we thought!
[YAMCHA yells]
[RECOOME yells]
You're right!
We can beat these guys!
Well, here goes nothing!
[GULDO grunts]
[CHIAOTZU giggles]
You see, Chiaotzu, if you
put your mind to something,
you always come out on top!
Yeah, but you have to admit
all that stuff that King Kai
taught us really came in handy!
Hey, I think they did
a number on Recoome.
Well, I say we
pull him out of here
and give him a proper burial!
[BURTER &amp; JEICE grunting]
That nap sure
was refreshing!
[RECOOME] And now it's
time for the Ginyu Force
to show you what
we're really made of.
Aaaaaaaa...
...tacckkkkk!
[RECOOME yells]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[JEICE] Burter!
Ginyu Force prepare...
...the Hurricane Attack!
No one can survive...
...the force of the Hurricane!
[BURTER &amp; JEICE yell]
[grunting]
[GULDO laughs]
[CHIAOTZU whimpers]
[GULDO yells]
That's it!
[GULDO grunts]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[thinking] Goku, I implore you!
We need your Spirited Bomb...
[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
Huh?!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
That's it, Goku...
It's up to you to
finish Frieza...
[GOKU grunting]
I'm almost done!
[GOKU] And then I'll defeat
Frieza once and for all!
[FRIEZA giggles]
So as not to be rude,
I'll finish with you first.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Hm?!
[FRIEZA growls]
[PICCOLO gasps]
Way to go...
And I didn't think you
guys had any power left...
Hmph.
I forgot about those other
insignificant, little bugs.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
No matter, I'll crush
them once I'm finished
with these two weaklings.
[FRIEZA laughs]
The end is at hand!
You and this entire
planet will be reduced
to nothing but dust!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOKU growls]
Goku...
Is it ready?
Yes!
It's complete!
C'mon!
Do it!
Daddy!
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Huh?!
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[BOTH gasp]
[FRIEZA] Nooo...!
[FRIEZA growls]
[PICCOLO] Hit the dirt!
No! That's...
impossible!
[FRIEZA growling]
[FRIEZA grunting]
[FRIEZA] I.. can't control it!
I-It's too powerful!
[grunting continues]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA grunting]
[GOHAN grunts]
[KRILLIN screams]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOKU screams]
[PICCOLO screams]
[BULMA screams]
[GINYU screams]
[BULMA] Help me, please!
[GINYU grunts]
[KING KAI] Hmm?! I'm
getting something!
[BOTH] Huh?
[KING KAI whimpers]
It finally
happened...
Goku defeated Frieza...
Goku has defeated Frieza!
Woo-hoo! Frieza's been defeated!
Ha, ha, woo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
So, he really
pulled it off!
You think the old kook
is telling the truth?
I'd say he's nuts!
Impossible!
Hurray for Goku!
Yeah, I second
that, Chiaotzu!
I knew he'd win!
Hey, Krillin!
[GOHAN laughs]
[KRILLIN] Thank goodness
you're safe!
You too!
So, Krillin, do you
think Frieza survived?
Hope not!
[GOHAN] Where's Piccolo?
And where's... my Dad?!
[NARRATOR] Finally Goku's
Spirit Bomb has done it's job!
Or has it?
Has Frieza been
totally destroyed?
And did the explosion
take out Piccolo and Goku?
Find out who survives, in
the next exciting episode of...
Dragon Ball Z!