[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
the evil wizard Babidi
was busy monitoring
the progress of Majin Buu,
the malevolent monster he plans
to unleash upon the Earth.
Once enough energy is collected,
the creature will be hatched
to destroy the planet.
But Babidi didn't count on
the Z Warriors dropping in
and spoiling his fiendish fun!
[NARRATOR] Goku and Gohan, along
with Vegeta and the Supreme Kai,
fought their way into
Babidi's spacecraft.
Now they must battle their way
through the multi-leveled ship
to get to the wizard.
But on each new level,
they must face one of
Babidi's fearsome fighters.
[NARRATOR]
It's not going to be easy...
Babidi is watching their every
move and gives his warriors
the advantage by casting spells
from deep inside his fortress.
[PUI PUI]
Enough!
[NARRATOR]
His dirtiest trick by far
was changing level one
of his ship into the
home planet of the
warrior Pui Pui.
But that didn't stop the
awesome power of Vegeta.
He easily defeated his
hapless opponent
with a quick blast of
Super Saiyan strength.
[SUPREME KAI]
Now I see...
[NARRATOR]
And with level two open,
the good guys were ready to
face their next challenger.
So, I wonder who's
behind that door there?
Hope he's tough!
[NARRATOR] Goku doesn't know
what he's in for!
He's about to face
the vicious Yacon.
Can Goku get the gang
to the next level?
Or is he about to become
lunch for a monster
with an appetite
for Super Saiyans?
[YACON growls]
[roars]
[YACON roars]
[GOKU]
Ah... Ugh...
Wow! He sure is an ugly one!
[laughs] Oh, yummy!
Who do I eat first?!
Why'd I have to get this guy?
Sure, he's big... but he
kinda looks dumb to me...
[gasps]
I know that monster!
I know who he is.
His name is Yacon!
You've met him before?
That's right...
He is one of the most feared
creatures in the universe
and he is extremely strong!
I don't think Goku will be
able to beat him on his own.
[VEGETA]
Hmph.
[BABIDI laughs]
That's it, Yacon!
Now, get his energy!
Give it to me!
Then we'll bring Majin Buu
back to life.
[BABIDI laughs]
[YACON chuckles]
[growls]
[GOKU]
Hmm.
[YACON grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[YACON growls]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU grunts]
[YACON grunts]
[gasps]
That was close!
[YACON laughs]]
So... He's a big one,
but he's quick!
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
That's what I was
trying to tell you...
And Goku can't beat him!
Huh? No. My dad should be
more than enough for that guy.
Just watch and see.
Watch and see...?
[YACON laughs]
You were very lucky...
But you won't
get away this time!
[sighs] I'd better watch it.
One slip and those claws
will tear me in two.
[BABIDI chuckles]
Look, he's afraid...
--[BABIDI laughs]
--Yes! He won't last long
against Yacon!
[BABIDI] I'd like to
watch him panic some more
but there is no time for that!
[BABIDI]
Can you hear me, Yacon?
Listen to me!
[YACON]
Hnn?!
[BABIDI] You're doing well,
my marvelous monster.
I'm proud of you,
do you know that?
With your help, Majin Buu
will be resurrected
sooner than expected.
I have a treat for you
that will help you
finish off these
intruders quickly.
How would you like to visit
your favorite planet?
The Planet of Darkness!
Would you like that, my pet?
[YACON gasps]
[DABURA]
I don't understand.
There is no need to help him
with this Earthling.
Yacon is strong enough
to beat him on his own.
Yes...
But it's all this fighting
inside the spaceship...
See, a shock could
wake Majin Buu and
we don't want him to be released
with insufficient energy, do we?
We must make sure he comes to
life with his utmost power.
Yes, of course. Good plan.
I know...
Now watch this!
Yacon doesn't need my help,
but he's going to get it!
[BABIDI yells]
[BABIDI]
Papara--Papaaaa!
[BABIDI cackles]
[GOKU gasps]
[SUPREME KAI, GOHAN gasp]
[YACON chuckles]
[GOKU]
Huh?
[GOKU grunts]
A stone? That hurt.
[GOKU]
Hey, what happened?
Who turned out the lights?
It's so dark
I can't see a thing!
[YACON growls]
[laughs]
Welcome to the
Planet of Darkness.
[YACON] You're scratching
your head, aren't you?
You can't see me,
but I can see you.
You can?
[GOHAN] Sounds like
he feels right at home.
[SUPREME KAI]
Yacon was born in this place.
It's at the far end
of the universe
where no light can reach it.
Thus, the Planet of Darkness.
[GOKU gasps]
[YACON]
You're mine now!
I'm gonna eat you!
[YACON yells]
[YACON]
Huh?
[GOKU shouts]
[YACON groaning]
[YACON]
Where is he?
Eat this!
[YACON gasps, grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
[YACON grunts]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Hey! Hey, can any of you tell
what's going on out there?!
Yes. Kakarot's winning.
[YACON yells, grunts]
[YACON groans]
You can see in the dark?
No. But then I don't
really need to.
I can sense your movements by
the subtle vibrations
in the air.
Oh yeah, I can smell
where you are, too.
[gasps]
[GOKU] I do have
one way I can see you.
Like this.
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
[gasps]
[BABIDI]
What is that guy up to?
He looks different than before!
Oh no, he-he's changing.
So what?
He's just emitting light.
You! Run and get me
my power meter at once!
I want to measure the
energy level of this guy!
Sir!
[GOKU]
Hmph.
[YACON whimpers]
Look at that!
Pretty impressive, huh?
Yacon! Come on out, stinky!
I seem to have found my
spare flashlight! See?
[YACON grunts]
[chuckles]
Well done.
So you've fixed it so I can
no longer hide in the dark.
Huh? I wonder why
he's being so calm?
[GUARD A]
Master Babidi!
[BABIDI]
I don't believe this!
Three thousand killis?!
How can an Earthling generate
3,000 killis of energy?!
It can't be...
With 300 killis, it's possible
to destroy a planet.
Three thousand?
I tell you a human with that
much power does not exist.
[BABIDI] Ugh. Do you think
this meter is broken?
If he really has
3,000 killis of energy...
Yacon doesn't even
have a chance.
My poor Yacon only
has 800 killis...
Do you know what that means?!
[CROWD grumbling]
So, Atne, when is this
thing gonna start?
I have no idea.
[yawns]
[GOHAN, TRUNKS
grunting, slurping]
[grunting continues]
[sighs]
More food, please!
[BOTH whimper, groan]
[PATRONS groan]
[GOTEN]
[TRUNKS slurps, sighs]
Now that was good!
It was great! Okay, Trunks!
I guess you're gonna take
care of the bill, aren'tcha?
Me? I don't have any cash.
But... We need money...
What about the competition?
Didn't you get the prize money
from when you won
the youth division?
I don't have it yet...
They told me they were gonna
give it out after the ceremony.
Oh, too bad!
[FRIAR B]
Hmm?
--Hey...
--Hey! Where're you goin', boys?
[GOTEN, TRUNKS gasp]
Oh no, they found us, Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
Run for it!
[FRIAR A]
Come back here!
And your noodles
tasted like dog hair!
[BOTH grunt]
Goten... What have
you been up to?
[laughs]
--[FRIAR A] Stop!
--[TRUNKS, GOTEN gasp]
You two kids better pay us
the money you owe us or else!
--[GOTEN yells]
--[TRUNKS] Oh, oh!
They'll take care
of that! See ya!
[ALL]
Hmm...?
[BOTH yell]
Time to feed!
[roars]
[GOKU]
Hm.
[yells]
[GOKU whimpers]
[SUPREME KAI, GOHAN gasp]
[YACON bellows]
Huh? What is he doing?
[YACON yells]
[YACON laughs, growls]
[roars]
Ah!
Oh no! Look, guys!
It's gone pitch black again!
Yes... Kakarot is
back to his normal state.
[sighs]
Yummy!
I've never eaten such a
rich and brilliant amount
of light before...
[GOKU]
What's that?
Yacon is a type of monster
that eats light energy.
Goku's a Super Saiyan; the
energy he is emitting
is like a delicacy to him!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN]
Hey, listen, Dad!
Don't become a
Super Saiyan again.
If you do, that monster
will eat your energy.
[GOKU]
Hm?
[laughs]
Very tasty.
The best light I have ever had.
I want some more of that!
Give me some more of it now!
So... he eats light.
[YACON grunts]
[sighs]
Oh. Okay... Are you ready
for the second course?
Yes!
You sure?
What on earth is Kakarot
trying to do now?
Dad, seriously!
Don't go Super Saiyan!
He's draining your energy!
Let's fight him together!
No way,
I fight alone, Gohan.
I don't need help.
[GOKU grunts]
[YACON laughs] I am going
to make a meal out of you!
Now come to me!
Has he gone crazy?!
Why does he insist
on fighting alone?
He knows he can't beat him!
Does he think this is
some kind of game?!
Let him do what he wants!
Kakarot wouldn't purposely get
eaten alive. He has a plan.
[roars]
[GOKU grunts]
[bellows]
[BABIDI]
What is Yacon doing?
He's sucking up all the
energy for himself!
He's wasting it!
He knows that unless he
inflicts some damage
to that guy, I can't give
his energy to Majin Buu!
[YACON roars]
[GOKU growls]
[roaring continues]
[YACON roars]
[YACON grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[gasps]
[GOKU growls, yells]
[YACON screams]
Look! Look, he blew up?!
All right! Dad won!
[VEGETA]
And with energy to spare.
Interesting...
[BABIDI wails]
Yacon?
[sighs]
Hey, the floor's opened up!
Come on, guys, let's go!
Yeah!
[whimpers]
[BABIDI whimpers]
Yacon went boom! Oh no!
Why did Yacon go boom?!
It was all a trap.
Yacon ate more energy
than he could handle.
And for his greed he suffered
the ultimate consequence.
But why? No!
My precious Yacon...
That guy... He's gone
and ruined everything...
Curse him!
A curse on all of them!
Way to go, Dad!
Guess that monster bit off
more than he could chew, huh?
[GOKU laughs]
Sure did.
[VEGETA thinking] It's obvious
now what Kakarot has gained
in these seven years
of training.
He's found a way
to push his limits
as a Super Saiyan even further!
[BABIDI] Dabura, that is
no ordinary Earthling,
that's for sure.
Master, don't worry.
He's mine now.
I'll take care of everything.
[gasps]
[DABURA laughs]
For stage three, I will be the
warrior that they must battle.
And you have my word that I will
fill Majin Buu with their energy
when I destroy
every one of them.
But, Dabura...
If you are beaten by them,
then who will protect me?!
You must promise me
that you'll win!
I'll win.
I am Dabura.
I am the Demon King.
I don't care how many killis
of energy they have.
There is no one in the universe
who can exceed my power.
[NARRATOR]
Goku is pumped
after putting a stop to
the menacing Yacon,
but he has no
idea of the danger
that's about to come
through that final door.
[GOKU]
So far so good!
I wonder who
Babidi'll send next?
Hey! You're up, Gohan!
All right!
[VEGITA]
Hmph.
[NARRATOR] With all of the fun
Goku and Gohan are having,
it seems the Supreme Kai
is the only one
who still remembers
their true mission.
And Dabura, with his ability to
turn people to stone
might be more than Gohan
can handle by himself.
Can Gohan summon the strength to
beat the Demon King
or is he destined to give up
his energy to Majin Buu?
Don't miss the
next Dragon Ball Z!
[GOHAN]
All right! I'm ready!