[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan gave Garlic Jr.
quite a beating.
And Krillin put him through
plenty of pain as well.
But with Piccolo see-sawing
between strength and weakness,
the evil giant
regained the upper hand.
In the resting place
of guardians past,
Kami took care
of the distraction
while Mr. Popo handled
the Sacred Water.
And the precious water
was spread over the earth,
to negate the horrible effect
of the Black Water Mist.
My plan!
[NARRATOR] Garlic Jr. was
incensed by this latest attempt
to foil his dark plans.
And in a terrible rage,
he decided to pull out
all the stops and
reopen the Dead Zone.
A horrible void of darkness
that sucks people into it
like a vacuum and
holds them in a timeless,
spaceless prison forever.
The Dead Zone
will swallow you up
and keep you for all eternity!
There's no escape!
[NARRATOR] With Piccolo's
power waning
and Krillin
weakened from battle,
it was up to Gohan
to protect them
from the deadly suction
of the Dead Zone!
But how long can the
little warrior hold on?
Find out, today!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
Yes! Know the lonely
horrors of the void!
[GOHAN grunts]
Gohan...
No! Fight, Kami...
[KAMI grunts]
[MR. POPO] Kami... Kami!
[MR. POPO wails]
[MR. POPO] Please! Let him go!
He... did it for them...
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[GOHAN grunts]
Wah!
[GOHAN growls]
Man! Whoa! Hold on tight, Gohan!
Sorry! We can't help too much!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[KRILLIN] Piccolo...
Don't give in, Piccolo.
You have to fight it!
Stay with us!
[KRILLIN] Yes, that's it!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[yelling]
[KAMI groans]
That's enough! Please!
[rumbling]
[MR. POPO screams]
[gasping]
What? How can this be?
The Dead Zone! Yes, Garlic Jr.
has reopened the Dead Zone!
[KAMI] Fools! By hurting me,
you're helping Garlic Jr.!
Are your egos so big that
you can't see past your nose?
[KAMI wails]
[KAMI grunts]
[thinking] Piccolo...
[PICCOLO grunts]
[KRILLIN] Piccolo!
[PICCOLO pants]
[GOHAN growls]
Seems you're having trouble
maintaining that, aren't you?
It won't be long now!
That little pimple
of a shield is going to pop
and the three of you
are going to ooze into
the Dead Zone like
the puss that you are!
[GARLIC JR. cackles]
[GOHAN] Guys! I'm slipping!
[KRILLIN] Oh, man! This is it!
We've got to
think of something fast!
Gohan! Don't give in!
We need all the time
that we can get!
No... Gohan... Makyo Star!
Say what?!
Huh?
Look! Blow up the Makyo Star!
It's the source of his power!
[KRILLIN] But he's barely
able to hold the shield!
I don't know, Piccolo...
That plan sounds
half baked to me...
No, it's fully baked.
It's the only way!
Uh, yeah, but-- Shoot!
If he lets go to attack,
we're goners!
Just do it, Gohan!
There's a whole world
of people down there
to consider!
Fools! I'll suck the whole
sanctuary up if I have to!
[GARLIC JR. roars]
[KRILLIN] Hold on,
Gohan, you can do it!
[GOHAN grunts]
[snarling]
[ALL] Huh?
[ALL coughing, yelling]
[murmuring]
[OLD MAN] Why are all
you people in my yard?
[OLD WOMAN] Oh, my gosh, look,
honey! There's one on the roof!
[GARLIC JR. cackles]
[GOHAN grunts]
Oh, what's the matter?
It's a little different
this time, isn't it, you brat?!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN] I'm not sure how
much longer I can hold this,
but I'll die before I give in!
Hey, don't talk like that!
Go for the win!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Destroy the Makyo Star, kid!
I can't! I just can't
let this shield down!
You guys mean too much
to me! I won't let you go!
Please! Do it!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN] I can't! I won't!
[KRILLIN growls]
Hey! Attack that star!
There's no way!
Piccolo's right, Gohan!
I don't like it
any more than you do,
but there's too much at stake!
There's a whole planet full
of people down there, Gohan!
This isn't about us!
I can't! No way!
Don't ask me to do that!
Never!
[MR. POPO] Please! He was
only trying to help!
[MR. POPO gasps]
[MR. POPO] Let him go!
Please! I beg of you!
Kami! Kami!
[MR. POPO whimpers]
[MR. POPO gasps]
Bye, Kami...
[KAMI] Hmm...?
What happened? I'm alive...
I think they
decided to let you go!
As long as they don't
change their minds again!
They've never done this before..
It's a great honor, Kami!
To be pardoned for coming here!
They've forgiven you!
[KAMI growls]
Oh, yeah? Well,
I haven't forgiven them!
Get a life, you
stubborn old fools!
[MR. POPO] Kami!
--[KAMI growls]
--[MR. POPO whimpers]
[BOTH grunt]
[BOTH yell]
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[GARLIC JR.] You're
starting to lose power!
I can feel it!
It won't be long now!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
Oh, man! What now?!
We're back home!
[KAMI] Huh...?
What? Kami?!
Hey! Kami's back!
--[PICCOLO] I know.
--Huh...?
[KRILLIN] Piccolo! You're okay!
Yeah, I'm fine!
Thanks to Kami,
better than ever!
So be it! You'll all diiieee!
[GARLIC JR. yells, laughs]
[grunting]
[MR. POPO wails]
[KAMI grunts]
[BOTH yell]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[PICCOLO] Here we go!
Piccolo!
[PICCOLO growls]
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
That's it! Embrace your destiny!
[MR. POPO whimpers]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[KAMI &amp; MR. POPO yell]
[PICCOLO using ESP] Kami, I
can't promise I'm going to
make it through this one!
I... understand...
[PICCOLO growls]
Yes! Come, Piccolo!
Come to your death!
Yes! Perfect!
Now just a little
bit closer, you fool!
How about a Belly-Blast?
[GARLIC JR. yells]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
Gohan, do it! Attack!
What about Krillin?
Gohan! I'm fine!
Search your feelings!
You know it's the
best thing to do right now!
Krillin! I can't!
I need to protect you!
Forget about me!
[KRILLIN yells]
Krillin, don't go!
[PICCOLO grunts]
What's wrong?!
Can't take the heat?!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[PICCOLO growls]
What a nice gift!
Here you go!
Right back at you, Piccolo!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[KRILLIN grunts]
Gohan, now!
Fire!
I've got you now!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GARLIC JR. gasps]
[GARLIC JR.] What?!
No! It can't be!
[GARLIC JR. screams]
[thinking] Kakarot, you're
so close I can smell you!
It won't be long now.
I'll become a Super Saiyan
and we'll see who's
really the strongest!
Huh...?
Huh?
[OOLONG &amp; PUAR groan]
[gasping, murmuring]
Uhh, hi there!
I'm sure you folks were
all wonderful subjects!
But, uh, I-I think it's time
that I, uh, abdicate the throne.
I was looking for Gohan!
How did I get way out here?
Boy is he going to be
in trouble when I find him!
Hey, you!
[gasping]
Yeah, you guys!
Don't you know
your moms are at home
worried sick about you?!
Get your butts home!
Piccolo...
You, too, Krillin...
Piccolo! Where are you?!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN] Krillin... Why didn't
you stay under the shield...?
[GOHAN] Huh?
[GOHAN gasps]
Kami! And Popo!
[GOHAN chuckles]
Oh my gosh! I can't
believe you made it!
Yes, by a whisker.
[MR. POPO] But my plants got
sucked into the Dead Zone...
[KRILLIN (muffled)] Gohan!
Have a little
respect, would ya?!
It hurts bad enough as it is!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN] Oh, man...
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Whoo! Hiya!
Man! I can't believe it!
Krillin, it's really you!
You made it!
[GOHAN laughs]
You made it! Thank goodness!
Yeah! Thank goodness
you saved us, Gohan!
[PICCOLO] Hey! Knock off the
mushy stuff, you sissies!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
[GOHAN] Uh?
[GOHAN] Oh my gosh... Piccolo...
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] Check him out!
Wow! Piccolo!
Yeah, well, thanks for blowing
up the Makyo Star, kid.
Because of you, Garlic
shriveled up like a raisin.
I see! So the lion's
share of his energy
was actually coming
from the Makyo Star!
Well, I'll be a green,
pointy-eared monkey's uncle!
With the star gone,
he's through!
I hope he can learn
to like the Dead Zone...
...since he's now
a permanent resident.
Piccolo! We did it ourselves!
We didn't even
need my dad this time!
We needed your dad
very much, kid!
And he was here the whole time!
What? Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure! He was
here, inside of you, Gohan!
Hey, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO] Yes?
Gosh... you're such
an incredible friend.
[PICCOLO] You too,
Gohan. You too...
[GOHAN chuckles]
[PICCOLO] He's okay.
He just needs a little rest.
[PICCOLO] Sleep well,
Gohan. I'm proud of you.
[NARRATOR] And so the planet
Earth was back to normal again.
Roshi and friends began
restoring his damaged house.
[OOLONG screams]
[NARRATOR] Krillin and Maron
traded-in for a convertible,
Gohan was being more
closely guarded than ever,
and Piccolo resumed his solitary
life of training and meditation.
And though he didn't
accept Kami's offer
to officially take over
as guardian of the Earth,
you can rest assured
that not much escapes
from Piccolo's
ever-watchful gaze.