[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku and Gohan finally returned
from their year of training,
and Goku traveled to the
tournament grounds to size up
his competition...
It was a tense moment
on the soon-to-be battlefield,
as the two super-powers
butted heads...
[GOKU] So leave everyone
else out of this
until we meet in the ring...
Agreed?
[NARRATOR] And that fight
is just nine days away!
[CELL] Well then, Goku...
You've just made my little
match even more interesting.
Well, if I were to
fight him right now,
I'm pretty confident that he
would beat me into the ground.
He still can use the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber once more.
[GOKU] Gohan and I
don't need a turn.
What?!
There's still
nine days left
so I think we'll just
train outside 'til then.
You're not serious?!
[NARRATOR]Goku means business,
but with just nine days left
until the
tournament begins,
he had better be ready
to take on Cell.
What could be the secret
to his confidence?
Find out today!
[PICCOLO] What do you mean
you're not going back in?
You mean you don't need to go?
[GOKU] Nope! There's no point!
But why?
You do realize you can still
spend another day in there.
I understand,
but I'd rather not go in.
It really won't help any.
[GOHAN gasps]
Training there takes
way too much out of me!
Hmph! I get it!
Little Kakarot finally admits
that he's too weak to continue!
Yeah right...
If you thinking torturing
your body training in there
is the same as training,
then go for it!
I wish you'd take
my advice, Vegeta.
Uh?
But... I know how
important it is to you
that you keep up with
my strength level.
So you'll be needing all
the time you can get.
Oh, really...?
Kakarot...
Call me crazy...
but you make it sound as if
you've become a great deal
stronger than I am.
Sure! I'm far above you.
What?!
[GOKU chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[GOKU] Well, good luck guys.
We'll catch you at the
tournament, okay?
Hmm?
Let's go.
Uh... Okay.
Gotta make a
quick pit stop!
Hey there, Korin!
What's up?
Hi, Korin!
How've you been?!
Ahh... I can't complain...
Hey, Yajirobe!
How ya doing?!
Oh, I know why you're here...
And if you think I'm
going to help you fight
in that stupid tournament,
then you can just forget it!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Thanks, Yajirobe,
but I wasn't going to ask you.
Like... I believe that!
Next, you'll tell me that you
just stopped by to say "hello"!
Well, you know I'm the best
kept secret weapon around!
Oh, shut it!
[GOHAN &amp; GOKU laugh]
So, seems the Earth
has really done itself
over good this time, huh?
What's your take on it?
Well... I was just
down there, Korin...
and I met with Cell
who I gotta say
looks pretty much
indestructible.
Then how come you
look so calm, Goku?
Spit it out! Did you discover
some great new secret
in the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber?
[GOKU laughs]
Actually, yes!
[thinking] What?
When did he do that?!
I was with him
the whole time!
[GOKU] Korin, the reason
I came here was to ask you
if you knew how strong
Cell really is.
[KORIN] Hmm... Up to now he
hasn't shown his full potential,
but, yes, I can
tell you, more or less.
Then, can you tell me
where I stand?
Here, Korin, I'm gonna
channel my power for you!
[TIEN] Okay, when Goku and
Gohan came out of the chamber
they were Super Saiyan right?
And yet, they seemed
so... so different!
Don't you think so, Piccolo?
From what I've seen, I think
they're still Super Saiyans.
But it appears they've learned
how to stay powered up
in their daily lives,
without creating a strain
on their energy supply.
That means...
they can transform
into a more powerful body
when they fight!
You're missing the point!
Huh?!
It's not about powering up.
The point is that they won't
have to power up
when they fight.
They can use all the energy
it would take to transform
to increase their stamina,
and then only go
higher if they need to.
Darn! It's so ingenious!
[thinking] How come
I didn't see that?!
I wasted all my energy because
I transformed too early
into a higher power level!
And that's the reason why
I wasn't able to beat Cell!
Why was I so stupid?!
[GOKU yells]
[KORIN screams]
[YAJIROBE whimpers]
[yelling continues]
[GOKU yelling]
[KORIN screams]
[yelling continues]
[TRUNKS gasps]
--[explosion]
--[PICCOLO yells]
[TIEN] That energy! What is it?!
It's... It's Goku.
[VEGETA growls]
[GOKU yelling]
[YAJIROBE screams]
[YAJIROBE grunting]
[yelling continues]
T-That's enough, Goku!
You're gonna wreck the tower!
[GOKU yelling]
[KORIN pants]
[YAJIROBE]
I'm losing my grip here!
Well, that was about
half of my power.
What d'ya think?
That... was only half?!
What's wrong with
people like you?
Will you not be happy until
you wreck the whole planet?!
[GOHAN thinking] Wow, Dad.
You were so busy training me...
How did you find the time
to get so strong?
I-I'm back...
[GOKU] So, how do I
stack up against Cell?
[KORIN] Hmm... That's hard
for me to answer...
[KORIN] Hmm. Well, I don't know
how precise I can be, but, uhhh.
To be blunt...
I'd have to say
Cell is stronger!
[GOHAN gasps]
Then, what are we
waiting around for?
Shouldn't we be, like,
planning our escape?
[GOKU laughs]
Just like I thought!
[GOHAN gasps]
Huh?
Yeah, I figured he
was more powerful!
Thanks, Korin. I owe you one!
Ready to go, Gohan?
Ah, yeah, sure...
Ah, sorry to bother you...
That Goku!
Who does he think he is anyway?!
[KORIN thinking] Yes. That's
exactly what I'm wondering...
If Goku knows that
he's inferior to Cell,
how do you explain the fact
that he's being so calm?
I don't understand it! Something
about this whole situation
smells awfully fishy to me!
[KORIN sniffs]
Wow. That was intense.
Yes, Tien. Yes it was.
But imagine if he had exerted
all of his energy at once!
I doubt any of us would
still be standing here now.
Good! That just means that
we'll have a better chance!
[VEGETA thinking]
Curse you, Kararot!
Always one step ahead of me!
No matter how much I progress,
you always seem to surpass me!
And now you've done it again!
You're always there,
laughing in my face!
Why won't you leave me alone?!
Piccolo!
Get inside the stupid
time chamber now!
Quit wasting time!
Let's get your Mom
and go on home.
We'll have some
time to relax there.
I figure we'll have
three days of rest,
plus three days
for some training,
and then three more days of
rest before the tournament.
[GOHAN] Hey Dad!
Can I ask you something?
Well, I've just been
wanting to know...
Do you think we have
a chance to beat Cell?
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU] Hey, let's not worry
about all that right now!
We've got nine days!
Let's kick back for a while!
[ROSHI] Hmm?
Hiya!
[ALL] Huh?!
[GOKU laughs]
Hey, everybody, you surprised?
I-It's Goku...
Yeah.
Are you really Goku?
Of course I am.
Who else were you expecting?
Then you must be Gohan.
But you've buffed up!
No kidding!
Aw, you think?
Goku. Has anyone told you about
the tournament
Cell's having yet?
Mm-hmm. Trunks told me about it.
And I just came back from
checking out Cell's new body!
Huh? You what??!
[KRILLIN] So?!
You can take him
no problem, right, Goku?!
I... dunno...
From what I saw of him,
he looks pretty tough.
He'd probably lick me!
[GOKU laughs]
[ALL] Huh?!
[YAMCHA laughs]
Okay, quit fooling
around, Goku.
You're kidding, right?!
No, not at all.
I'm dead serious.
[YAMCHA gasps]
So how come you're
in such a good mood?!
You're hiding
something, aren't you?
[GOKU chuckles]
That's for me to know.
Where's ChiChi?
We've actually come
to take her home with us.
I think I heard her
upstairs somewhere.
Hey! Hey ChiChi!
[CHICHI] Goku?!
Is that really you?!
I was so worried about you,
I was just abo--
[CHICHI gasps]
Hi, honey! it's time
to take you home.
[CHICHI yelps]
Yeah, Mom. Let's go!
But what happened? Where is
my sweet, little Gohan?
I'm right here, Mom.
[GOKU laughs
Ah, babe, you crack me up!
Calm down... Calm down...
[CHICHI groans]
[CHICHI shrieks]
[ALL grunt]
What happened to your
beautiful black hair?!
Who gave you
permission to dye it?!
[GOHAN grunts]
It's not dyed, it's just--
[CHICHI wails]
My sweet, little Gohan
has become a punker!
[sobbing]
No, it's not like that!
Well, now. It's time for
my warm-up exercises.
[thinking] It's rare that I get
to make use of Frieza
and his father's
wonderful genes.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Perhaps those
miserable humans
would appreciate
a little light show.
Huh...? Wow, pretty!
[WOMAN] What's going on ?!
[MAN] Asteroids!
Run for your lives!
Goku!
[CHICHI] Goku?
[CHICHI] Gohan! Gohan!
Now... where did
they disappear to?
[GOHAN] This is nice, Dad.
[GOKU] Yeah...
Dad, you know what?
I'm so happy.
[GOKU] I'm glad you think so.
A long time ago,
you promised me
that we'd go fishing.
[GOKU] Hmm, really?
When did I promise that?
[GOHAN] C'mon! You mean,
you don't remember?
No, I don't.
Hey. I remember.
[GOKU] Krillin?
Let me jog your memory.
[KRILLIN] I was standing just
like this, and I said...
[PAST GOKU] Huh?
Hey, buddy.
I feel bad that you always have
to take off and defend us, but,
promise me you'll
come back in one piece?
Promise!
What about me?!
[GOKU] Hey, Gohan.
I promise that
when I get back,
we'll head out and go fishing!
Ohhh.
Well... Huh?
Yeah, right, I remember!
In a lot of ways, that
seems so long ago...
But at the same time,
it's like nothing's changed!
[GOKU] Those memories
keep us close.
You'll never forget them, right?
[GOHAN] Never.
Goku... I, ahh... got a bit
of a confession to make...
Like what?
I let Cell morph into
his ultimate form!
It's my fault because I
destroyed 18's controller!
Hey, don't sweat it, Krillin.
I know you wouldn't have
broken that controller
unless you had a good reason!
There was a reason... But I
feel like I let you down...
Don't be silly.
We're best friends, remember?
Yeah, me too!
I don't know what we'd
do without you, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Ahh,
you're just saying that.
You two are way stronger
than I'll ever be,
so I wouldn't be
surprised if one day,
you just both moved on...
[GOKU] That has
nothing to do with it!
Have you forgotten all the time
we spent together
back at Master Roshi's?
Now look who's
losing his memory!
Hold on... Maybe if I
just... concentrate...
[GOKU laughs]
Knock it off!
[KRILLIN wails]
Help... Goku... Help... me...
Grab my hand! C'mon!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[GOKU yells]
[KRILLIN laughs]
I got you good, sucker!
I should win an award for that!
Yeah, you're real funny...
[GOHAN laughs]
Ahh... I love it!
[thinking] I suppose Goku really
hasn't changed that much.
At least on the inside...
[thinking] Look at them!
Super Saiyan even
when they sleep!
This must be part of
Goku's secret training!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[thinking] I bet he
can sense everything
that's going on for miles!
[KRILLIN thinking] Which means
if I chucked this rock at him,
he'll just zap it
into a million pieces
without even opening his eyes.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[thinking] This is
going to be so cool!
[GOKU screams]
What'd ya do that for?!
I... didn't... mean...
Darn it! If that's your
idea of a joke,
then you've lost your mind!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Ahhh... That was good!
Gohan, time to do your homework.
'Kay!
Huh?!
[thinking] Man, if this is what
Goku meant by training
in the outside world,
we're in a whole lotta trouble!
Ahh... I'm full now...
[NARRATOR] Krillin's
may be on to something!
This doesn't look anything like
a training schedule
for the hopeful-savior
of the planet.
And with only nine days left
before the Cell Games begin,
there isn't much room for error.
The day is fast approaching,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!