(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
[NAOTSUGU, MUFFLED]
SO THE BIG‐SCALE FESTIVAL
STARTS TOMORROW, HUH?
EVERYBODY'S PRETTY FREAKING
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
[NYANTA] WELL, IT'S OUR FIRST
FESTIVAL IN AKIHABARA, HUH?
SINCE WE ALL DECIDED TO
MAKE THIS HAPPEN, HMM.
MANY OF THE GUILDS DECIDED TO
PITCH IN AND MAKE IT GREAT.
YOU AIN'T LYING.
(SMASH LAUGHING)
[NAOTSUGU] JUST HEARING
THERE'S A FESTIVAL
MAKES A LOT OF PEOPLE
WANT TO MAKE SOMETHING.
[MARIELLE] AH.
[NAOTSUGU]
DECORATIONS?
[NYANTA] YOU GOT YOURSELF
QUITE A HAUL THERE.
[MARIELLE] I, LIKE, CAN'T EVEN
FIT THEM INTO MY MAGIC BAG!
[NAOTSUGU] I HEARD THAT THE
CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE IS
GONNA BE SELLING WINTER
CLOTHES OR SOMETHING.
[MARIELLE] WE'RE ALSO
DOING A FASHION SHOW.
[NAOTSUGU] SWEET!
[NYANTA] OH, I LIKE THAT.
[MARIELLE] WE'RE DOING IT
ALL TOMORROW, SO, LIKE,
WE'VE GOT TO GET
EVERYTHING READY TODAY.
DON'T WORK TOO
HARD, MARIELLE.
I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE BRINGING
BACK THE CRESCENT BURGER, HMM?
[MARIELLE] YOU'VE GOT IT!
SO WHAT ARE YOU GUYS GONNA DO
WHILE ALL THIS IS GOING ON?
[NYANTA] I'LL BE CONTENT
JUST ROAMING AROUND,
BROWSING THE SHOPS. MYEAH.
[NAOTSUGU] WELL, I'M
GONNA EAT. AND THEN I'M
GONNA EAT SOME MORE!
AND AKATSUKI
AND THE OTHERS?
[NYANTA] I DON'T THINK THEY'VE
MENTIONED ANY PLANS, HMM?
[NAOTSUGU] WELL, I'M SURE
THEY'LL FIND SOMETHING TO DO.
[KANAKO] HERE YOU GO.
TAKE ONE. HERE YOU GO.
BRING A FRIEND AND
COME AS A COUPLE.
HM!
ALL RIGHT! I'VE GOT
TO INVITE SHIROE!
[SHIROE] YOU ARE AS BIG A PART
OF THIS AS ANY ONE OF US.
I MEAN IT.
HM...
(SHIROE YAWNS)
(WIND BLOWS)
[SHIROE] AHH!
(GROWLS)
COME ON! ARE YOU
FREAKING KIDDING ME?! AAH!
HELLO, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] UH!
[HENRIETTA] ARE YOU SHUTTING
YOURSELF UP IN HERE AGAIN?
[SHIROE] BETWEEN HANDLING
OUR PAPERWORK AND TRYING
TO LEARN MORE,
I DON'T THINK I'VE
EVER BEEN SO BUSY.
[SHIROE] HMM...
[HENRIETTA] OK, WELL, ARE YOU
EATING ENOUGH, SLEEPING ENOUGH?
[SHIROE] YEAH, I'M
DOING WHAT I CAN.
I TOOK A 15‐MINUTE NAP,
AND I ATE ALMOST 2 HOURS AGO.
[HENRIETTA] UH, OKEY‐DOKEY!
THAT'S FINE, THEN!
HERE IS THE INFORMATION
YOU REQUESTED. AHEM.
[SHIROE] THANKS FOR THAT.
I REALLY DIDN'T WANT TO
PUT YOU OUT, THOUGH.
ALL YOU HAD TO DO WAS GIVE ME
A CALL, AND I WOULD HAVE COME.
[HENRIETTA] SO YOU SAY,
BUT WOULD YOU HAVE REALLY
ACTUALLY DONE IT?
YOU SEE, I'VE HEARD YOU'VE
BEEN LOCKED IN THIS ROOM
HERE FOR AGES UPON AGES.
SO I WANTED TO CHECK AND MAKE
SURE YOU WERE STILL ALIVE.
OK, YOU GOT ME. HOW'S THAT
SCALE FESTIVAL LOOKING?
[HENRIETTA] KARASHIN
IS DOING GREAT.
I MEAN, HE'S REALLY
TAKEN CHARGE OF THE EVENT.
[SHIROE] THE GUY
DOES GOOD WORK.
[HENRIETTA] YOU SHOULD
DO YOURSELF A FAVOR
AND TRY TO TAKE A BREAK
DURING THESE NEXT 3 DAYS.
YEAH, I SUPPOSE
I REALLY SHOULD.
THE FESTIVAL IS BOUND
TO BE PRETTY LOUD.
I CAN'T WORK
LIKE THAT.
[HENRIETTA] OH, THAT
IS JUST NONSENSE!
[SHIROE] HUH?
[HENRIETTA] THIS IS A WONDERFUL
OPPORTUNITY FOR YOU TO BECOME
CLOSER TO YOUR GUILDMATES.
AND SINCE LOG HORIZON
IS OFFICIALLY ONE OF THE
GUILDS OF THE ROUND TABLE,
YOU WILL BE OUT THERE MAKING
THE EVENT FUN AND DELIGHTFUL
AND SUPER!
UH, I GUESS
I'LL TRY.
THAT'S IT.
BE A GOOD BOY.
AGH, SURE!
[HENRIETTA] AKATSUKI AND
MINORI ARE SO FREAKING CUTE,
I'M LOSING MY MIND!
I DON'T THINK I'LL BE
ABLE TO CONTROL MYSELF!
WHAT'S THAT?
IT'S AN ADORABLE
AKATSUKI DOLL
ADORABLE AKATSUKI
GAVE ME!
(AKATSUKI SHUDDERS)
[SHIROE] IT'S SO CREEPY.
AS LONG AS I HAVE BOTH
OF MY AKATSUKIS,
I DON'T THINK I'LL
EVEN NEED TO EAT!
[HENRIETTA] THEY SAY THAT A MAN
DOES NOT LIVE BY BREAD ALONE.
BUT WITH BREAD AND FANTASIES,
YOU CAN ACCOMPLISH ALMOST
ANYTHING YOU EVER WANTED TO DO!
WHOA, OH, WHOA!
(SHIROE CHUCKLES)
[SHIROE]
SHE'S GOT A POINT.
I GUESS IT WOULDN'T HURT FOR ME
TO GET OUT THERE AND BE SOCIAL.
I'M PROBABLY GONNA HAVE
TO BURN THE MIDNIGHT OIL
AFTER ALL THOSE REPORTS COME
IN AFTERWARDS ANYWAY.
BESIDES, I'M STILL WAITING FOR
SOMETHING TO GO DOWN IN MINAMI.
[AKATSUKI] UH, M‐MY LORD?
[SHIROE] UH, AAH!
OH! HEY THERE!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?!
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?!
WELL, UM, NO.
WOULD YOU...
LIKE A RED BEAN BUN?
[SHIROE] EHH...
[SHIROE] AH...
IT'S BEAUTIFUL TODAY!
IT FEELS LIKE I HAVEN'T
SEEN THE SUN IN FOREVER.
[AKATSUKI] THIS IS FOR YOU.
[SHIROE] HUH? YOU SURE?
[SHIROE] PEOPLE ARE CHARGING AN
ARM AND A LEG FOR THOSE HERE.
[AKATSUKI] I GOT THEM FOR YOU.
[SHIROE] THANK YOU.
[SHIROE] AH! MM!
[BOTH] MM!
[SHIROE] THAT'S GOOD!
IT'S BEEN A REALLY LONG TIME.
HUH?
WH‐WHAT'S WRONG?
[AKATSUKI] YOU'VE GOT BEAN
PASTE ON YOUR FACE.
[SHIROE] HUH? OH.
HEH, THANKS!
[AKATSUKI] YOU'VE BEEN LOOKING
A LITTLE PALE LATELY.
[SHIROE] WHATEVER. I'M FINE.
[AKATSUKI] OH, REALLY?
[SHIROE] MM‐HMM.
[AKATSUKI] SO, MY LORD...
SO WHAT'S BEEN
BOTHERING YOU ANYWAY?
WHAT? UH, WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO DURING THE FESTIVAL?
THE FESTIVAL? HONESTLY, I'M
PROBABLY GONNA HAVE TO HELP OUT.
AT LEAST, I THINK THAT'S
WHAT HENRIETTA SAID.
OK.
[AKATSUKI]
I HAVE A QUESTION.
[SHIROE] HMM?
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, ARE
YOU A FAN OF EATING CAKE?
[SHIROE] HUH?
[MINORI] TA‐DA!
[AKATSUKI] GAH!
[SHIROE] WHAT'S THAT?
[MINORI] WELL, IT'S
SOMETHING THAT'S GOING ON
AT THE FESTIVAL TOMORROW.
YOU WANT TO GO EAT SOME
YUMMY CAKE WITH ME?
[SHIROE] IT'S A
CAKE BUFFET?
WELL, I FIGURED YOU
WERE THE KIND OF GUY
WHO LIKES SWEET THINGS.
FROM THE WAY HE EATS
HIS RED BEAN BUNS,
I WOULD SAY YES.
WELL, I CERTAINLY
DON'T DISLIKE THEM!
[AKATSUKI]
WE SHOULD GO,
MY LORD.
AND, WELL, IF WE GO AS
A COUPLE, IT'S FREE!
[MINORI] IT'S FREE,
TOTALLY FREE. LET'S GO!
[AKATSUKI] AH...
(MINORI GASPS)
[SHIROE] WHOA, WHOA! HANG ON...
[MINORI] MASTER SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD!
(SHIROE GROANING)
(HAMMERING)
[SHIROE, THINKING] WHAT A
QUANDARY. WHAT DO I DO?
OH! I KNOW!
[MINORI] HMM, MAYBE NOT THIS.
[ISUZU] MINORI?
THERE'S A PRE‐FESTIVAL DANCE
GOING ON TONIGHT. COME WITH ME.
UH, WHAT YOU GOT
GOING ON THERE?
HMM. I'LL BE GOING OUT
WITH SHIROE TOMORROW,
BUT I DON'T REALLY
KNOW WHAT TO WEAR.
YOU'RE GOING OUT
WITH HIM? SERIOUSLY?
HE NEVER LETS HIMSELF
GO OUT ANYWHERE!
(NAOTSUGU SNORING)
MAYBE HE COMES OUT FROM
BEHIND THAT DESK OF HIS
AND LETS HIMSELF HAVE SOME
FRESH AIR ONCE A WEEK.
SO WHERE ARE YOU
GUYS GONNA GO?
WE'RE GOING TO
A CAKE BUFFET.
WAIT! YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING ME.
DOES HE EVEN
LIKE CAKE?
[MINORI] I THINK SO. IT SAYS
IF YOU WIN THIS CONTEST,
YOU GET 2 TICKETS TO
THE TWILIGHT BANQUET
WITH PRINCESS RAYNESHIA ON
THE SECOND DAY OF THEIR EVENT.
[ISUZU] WHAT? REALLY?
[MINORI] YOU KNOW, A LOT OF
PEOPLE DON'T TRUST SHIROE.
THEY SAY THEY CAN'T TELL
WHAT HE'S REALLY THINKING.
THEY ALWAYS FEEL LIKE
HE'S UP TO SOMETHING.
BUT HE'S A
REALLY NICE GUY.
AND IT BUGS ME WHEN
THEY SAY THAT ABOUT HIM.
AND I WANT TO SHOW
THEM HE'S A LOT MORE
THAN JUST A VILLAIN
BEHIND GLASSES.
(ISUZU CHUCKLES)
OH! THIS IS
JUST TOO GOOD!
[ISUZU] YOU'VE GOT
TO LET ME HELP!
I SHALL BE YOUR
FASHION COORDINATOR!
OH, THAT'S SO
NICE OF YOU.
THANKS, ISUZU!
(AKATSUKI GROANS)
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
WHY DOES MINORI HAVE TO PUT
SO MUCH STINKING
PRESSURE ON ME?
SHE'S JUST A MIDDLE‐SCHOOLER,
FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
UGH. HE TREATS ME LIKE
A MIDDLE‐SCHOOLER SOMETIMES.
IT DOESN'T SEEM FAIR.
BUT IS IT MY LORD'S FAULT FOR
TREATING ME LIKE A KID? IS IT?
WELL...
I COULDN'T DO
THIS WITHOUT YOU.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
MY LORD NEVER JUDGED ME
BASED ON MY APPEARANCE
OR EXPERIENCE LEVEL.
HE JUST ACCEPTED ME.
HE ACCEPTED ME FOR
EXACTLY WHO I AM.
MY LORD SAID THAT
HE'D ATTEND THE BUFFET
WITH BOTH MINORI AND ME.
BUT IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
FOR JUST COUPLES ONLY.
SO WE SHOULD END UP
ALONE AT SOME POINT.
(GASPS)
WAIT A SECOND. IS THIS...
IS THIS A DATE?! AAH!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
WHAT EVER SHOULD I WEAR?!
(CLATTER)
[NYANTA] WHO'S BRINGING
ALL THAT RUCKUS?
[NAOTSUGU] WHO KNOWS?
IT'S AKATSUKI. SHE'S CRAZY.
[AKATSUKI] I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO CUTE CLOTHES‐‐
NOTHING SOFT, NOTHING PRETTY.
I NEED SOME SERIOUS HELP.
[HENRIETTA] OH!
[MARIELLE] ARE YOU OK?
[HENRIETTA] OH, MY GOD.
I JUST FELT A DISTURBANCE!
MY LOVELY AKATSUKI
NEEDS MY ASSISTANCE!
(AKATSUKI SHUDDERS)
[HENRIETTA]
AKATSUKI, I'M COMING!
[AKATSUKI] I SHOULD
PICK SOMETHING MYSELF.
[KARASHIN] NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S GONNA BE WAY
TOO EXPENSIVE.
NO, I'M AFRAID I CAN'T DO THAT.
THE COUNCIL DOESN'T REALLY
LIKE TO PLAY FAVORITES.
YOUR LOCATION IS
DETERMINED BY LOTTERY.
AND THAT'S NOT
GOING TO CHANGE.
SO, UH, YOU'RE DOING
ALL THIS BY YOURSELF?
I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
THIS WHOLE THING'S LIKE
A GIANT BUSINESS CONVENTION.
WHAT IS ALL
THIS STUFF?
I ASKED FOR EVERYONE
WHO'S INTERESTED TO
SUBMIT THEIR PROPOSALS.
I WANT TO CHECK FOR
ANY DANGEROUS ITEMS.
HMM, MAN. THAT IS
A LOT OF CRAP.
[KARASHIN]
I KNOW, RIGHT?
PLUS, A BUNCH OF MERCHANTS
FROM THE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND ARE COMING AS WELL.
[MICHITAKA] REALLY?
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE
THIS LITTLE FESTIVAL OF OURS
HAS GOTTEN A WHOLE LOT BIGGER
THAN WE EVER THOUGHT, HUH?
[KARASHIN] THE NEXT FEW
DAYS ARE GONNA BE NUTS.
WELL, LOOKIE HERE.
[MICHITAKA] HMM?
(MICHITAKA GASPS)
DON'T DO THAT!
[AKATSUKI] I NEED YOUR HELP.
[MICHITAKA] WELL, THAT'S RARE.
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
[KARASHIN] IS SOMETHING
WRONG, AKATSUKI?
[AKATSUKI] I NEED
SOMETHING...
I MUST ACQUIRE FASHION!
[BOTH] HUH?
(CROWD CHATTER)
ALL RIGHT.
SHIROE OF LOG HORIZON.
[KANAKO] AND, WAIT...
TWO OTHERS?
[MINORI] THAT'S RIGHT.
[AKATSUKI] MM‐HMM.
[SHIROE] I'M TERRIBLY SORRY
TO PUT YOU OUT LIKE THIS.
[KANAKO] OH, RIGHT.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND.
LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE YOUR HANDS FULL.
BUT BEST OF
LUCK TO YOU!
[SHIROE] HUH?
[SHIROE, THINKING]
WHAT DID SHE MEAN BY THAT?
HUH?
IT REALLY IS ALL
COUPLES HERE TODAY.
MM! I CAN'T WAIT TO START.
[SHIROE, THINKING] WELL, I'M
DEFINITELY GLAD THEY LET ALL
THREE OF US DO THIS.
[AKATSUKI AND MINORI]
REALLY? ALL THREE OF US?
[SHIROE] YES. I JUST GOT THE OK
FROM THE EVENT ORGANIZER.
SO WE SHOULD BE FINE.
BUT WE'LL NEED TO EAT 12
BETWEEN THE THREE OF US, OK?
I KNOW WE CAN DO IT!
(MINORI AND AKATSUKI
MOAN WEAKLY)
[MINORI] SURE THING! WE'LL WIN
AS A TEAM AND GO TO THE FINALS,
RIGHT, AKATSUKI?
YEAH.
[SHIROE, THINKING] TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T THINK I COULD HAVE
EATEN HERE TWICE ANYWAY.
BUT I'M HAVING THE STRANGEST
FEELING RIGHT NOW.
WHAT IS THIS...
PRESSURE?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE NEVER SEEN YOU
DRESSED LIKE THAT.
[AKATSUKI] U‐UH!
[SHIROE] THAT'S A REALLY
NICE KIMONO. WHAT'S UP?
[AKATSUKI] WELL, I, UH...
I HAD A GUILD CALLED KIMONO
KOMACHI MAKE IT FOR ME.
DOES... DOES IT LOOK OK?
[SHIROE] WELL‐
[AKATSUKI] IT'S NOT FOR
GRADUATION! IT'S FASHION!
[SHIROE] OH. IT'S A‐A GRACEFUL
AND REALLY LOVELY OUTFIT, YEAH!
[AKATSUKI]
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
[MINORI] YEAH! IT'S
REALLY CUTE ON YOU.
[SHIROE] AND YOU
LOOK GOOD, TOO.
[MINORI] AH!
(MINORI CHUCKLES)
WELL, YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO SAY THAT.
ISUZU HELPED ME LOOK
FOR SOME NEW CLOTHES.
OH, YEAH,
IS THAT RIGHT?
[MINORI] YEAH.
SHE TOOK ME
TO A WHOLE BUNCH
OF DIFFERENT STORES.
WE OUGHT TO MAKE IT
A GIRLS' DAY OUT
FOR ALL THREE OF
US SOMETIME.
[AKATSUKI] OH. MM‐HMM.
ISUZU KNOWS A TON
ABOUT CLOTHES.
SHE SHOWED ME A
LOT WHEN WE WENT.
(MINORI CHUCKLES)
[MINORI]
THAT LOOKS SO GOOD!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, I'M FEELING
REALLY GOOD ABOUT THIS!
[MINORI] I'M SO EXCITED!
THOSE CAKES ARE GORGEOUS!
[SHIROE] HERE WE GO! WE'RE
GONNA HAVE TO EAT 4 OF THOSE
CAKES APIECE, ALL RIGHT?
OK, GUYS, ENJOY!
[SHIROE] HUH? WHAT?
[KANAKO] DIG IN!
[SHIROE] WAIT! ARE YOU CRAZY?!
THOSE CAKES ARE HUGE!
IT'S JUST A LITTLE PRESENT
FOR YOU FROM MY GUILD.
[SHIROE]
THANK YOU SO MUCH...
[SHIROE] OK...
[SHIROE] MIGHT AS WELL
START AT THE BEGINNING.
[MINORI] LET'S DO THIS!
[AKATSUKI] LET'S DIG IN.
[ALL] MM!
IT'S GREAT!
[AKATSUKI] YEAH, MY LORD.
DO YOU REALLY LIKE IT?
[SHIROE] WHAT ARE
YOU DOING?!
I'M SERVING YOU,
MY LORD.
OK, BUT NOT A WHOLE
FREAKING CAKE!
[MINORI] OH, LET ME GO AHEAD
AND CUT IT UP FOR YOU.
[SHIROE] THAT ISN'T GONNA
MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
[MALE] THAT'S NOT FAIR.
HE GOT TO BRING 2.
[FEMALE] UNBELIEVABLE...
[MALE] IS HE TRYING
TO SHOW OFF?
[SHIROE, THINKING] OH, MY GOD.
IS THAT HOW THIS LOOKS?
THERE'S NO NEED TO GET THE
GIRLS TOO INVOLVED IN THIS.
I OBVIOUSLY CAN'T
GET UPSET RIGHT NOW.
BUT I SHOULD MINIMIZE
THE DAMAGE AND RETREAT.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD...
(SHIROE GASPS)
[AKATSUKI] HERE YOU GO.
[SHIROE] UH! YOU REALLY
WANT ME TO KEEP EATING?
[AKATSUKI] OF COURSE,
MY LORD. SAY "AHH."
(SHIROE MOANS)
COME ON OR IT'S
GONNA FALL OFF.
[AKATSUKI] IS IT GOOD, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] MM‐HMM!
[MINORI] MASTER SHIROE,
SAY "AHH."
(SHIROE GROANS)
TRY THIS ONE, TOO!
[SHIROE] UH...
[MINORI] IS IT GOOD?
(AKATSUKI GROANS SOFTLY)
[SHIROE] OH, YEAH,
IT'S GOOD, BUT...
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I SWEAR I'D RATHER FIGHT
A DOZEN RAID BOSSES AT ONCE
AND RISK DYING A DOZEN TIMES.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD...
THERE'S STILL
MORE. AHH!
AND ANOTHER. AHH!
HELP ME...
[AKATSUKI] AHH!
[MINORI] AHH!
[GIRLS] AHH!
[SHIROE] FOR THE LOVE
OF GOD, STOP THE CAKE!
(SHIROE GROANS)
[KANAKO] THANK YOU!
COME BACK AND SEE US. BYE...
[MINORI]
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU'D HAVE
TO PAY FOR EVERYTHING.
[SHIROE] WE COULDN'T
EAT THEM ALL,
SO I DIDN'T HAVE A LOT
OF CHOICE ABOUT THAT.
ARE YOU GOING HOME
TO REST, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] I WAS GOING
TO LOOK AROUND A BIT,
BUT THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
(SHIROE GROANING)
[MINORI] UM, YOU TWO
GO ON WITHOUT ME.
I NEED TO MAKE A STOP
BEFORE GOING BACK.
[ROBOT] I LIKE YOUR OUTFIT.
[MALE] THANK YOU!
[ROBOT] IT LOOKED REALLY GREAT.
I LIKE IT. I LIKE YOUR OUTFIT.
[MINORI, THINKING] I'M SAD WE
DIDN'T GET A CHANCE TO MEET
THE PRINCESS AT THE
TWILIGHT BANQUET,
BUT SHIROE WENT AND
ATE ALL THAT CAKE.
I'VE GOT TO THANK
HIM SOMEHOW.
DANDELION BARLEY TEA IS GOOD
FOR INDIGESTION, RIGHT?
(SHIROE MOANING)
[SHIROE] MY STOMACH...
WHO HEARD OF 3 PEOPLE
EATING 12 WHOLE CAKES?
SOMEBODY'S GONNA PAY FOR THIS.
WAIT. I KNOW.
[SOUJIRO] A CAKE BUFFET?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT]
OH, YEAH. AND IT'S REALLY
AWESOME. YOU SHOULD GO.
IT'LL BE FREE.
[SOUJIRO] THAT SOUNDS GREAT!
I'LL DEFINITELY GO.
I MEAN, WHO
DOESN'T LIKE CAKE?
THANKS FOR LETTING
ME KNOW, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] OF COURSE!
[SHIROE, THINKING] WITH ALL
HIS GIRLS, HE'LL WEIGH 600
POUNDS BEFORE HE'S DONE.
EVEN WITH ALL THE ATTENTION
THOSE GIRLS GIVE HIM,
SOUJIRO DOESN'T SEEM TO HAVE A
PROBLEM RUNNING HIS GUILD.
AND NAOTSUGU AND CHIEF NYANTA,
THEY HAVE THOSE LEADERSHIP
QUALITIES I LOOK FOR IN
A GUILD MASTER, TOO.
THERE'S A PRESENCE
TO IT I DON'T HAVE.
MAYBE HENRIETTA'S RIGHT,
AND THE OPPORTUNITY'S RIGHT
HERE IN FRONT OF ME.
JUST MAKE THE TIME AND
SPEND IT WITH EVERYONE.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD.
[SHIROE] HUH?
[SHIROE] WHAT?! WHEN THE
HECK DID YOU GET HERE?!
[AKATSUKI] A SECOND AGO.
[SHIROE] OH. IS SOMETHING WRONG?
[AKATSUKI] NO.
THERE IS NOTHING
WRONG, MY LORD.
(FIREWORK REPORT)
[AKATSUKI] THE TOWN IS EVEN
MORE LIVELY THAN USUAL.
[SHIROE] THAT'S WHAT
FESTIVALS ARE FOR.
WHEN WE FIRST GOT HERE,
I WOULDN'T HAVE IMAGINED THINGS
BEING LIKE THIS AT ALL.
[AKATSUKI] YEAH.
[SHIROE] YOU'RE KIND OF QUIET.
[AKATSUKI] I'M ALWAYS QUIET.
I'M A NINJA.
[SHIROE] NOT LIKE THIS.
MY LORD...
HM?
DO YOU, WELL,
DO YOU...
DO YOU NOT
REALLY LIKE CAKE?
UH...
OR DID... OR DID YOU
NOT HAVE ANY FUN?
[SHIROE] I WOULDN'T
SAY THAT.
ANYWAY, I'M SORRY
WE DIDN'T ADVANCE.
[AKATSUKI]
THAT DOESN'T
MATTER TO ME.
IT WAS MINORI
WHO WANTED TO GO.
[SHIROE] I GUESS.
[SHIROE] LET ME ASK YOU,
I DON'T SUPPOSE YOU HAD
A PROBLEM WITH THE CAKE.
[AKATSUKI] HM?
[SHIROE] IT SEEMS LIKE I
WAS DOING ALL THE EATING.
I DON'T THINK EITHER
OF YOU HAD ANY OF IT.
I GUESS I...
I WASN'T THERE FOR THE WHOLE
CAKE‐EATING PART OF IT.
[SHIROE] OK...?
[AKATSUKI] I FIND IT DIFFICULT
TO HAVE A CONVERSATION
WITH YOU, MY LORD.
[SHIROE] I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY, YOU KNOW?
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU GIVE ME
A LOT TO WORK WITH, AKATSUKI.
[AKATSUKI] THAT'S NOT TRUE!
I HAVE ALL SORTS OF
THINGS TO DISCUSS.
[SHIROE] OK, PICK A SUBJECT
FOR US AND LET'S TALK.
[AKATSUKI] UH, HMM...
[SHIROE, THINKING] MAYBE I
SHOULDN'T HAVE PUSHED IT.
[SHIROE] UM, I DIDN'T MEAN...
I'M SORRY. HEY! WAIT!
[AKATSUKI] I LIKE TO
DO THIS. IT'S FUN.
[SHIROE] UH...
[SHIROE] THIS IS
REALLY FUN FOR YOU?
[AKATSUKI] IT IS FOR ME.
[SHIROE] UM...
[SHIROE, THINKING]
IS THIS PART OF THE WHOLE
LORD AND SERVANT THING SHE
LIKES DOING WITH ME?
(AKATSUKI CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
[SHIROE] SO THIS IS FUN? REALLY?
[AKATSUKI] YES, IT IS.
[SHIROE] OKEY‐DOKEY...
(FOOTSTEPS AND PANTING)
[MINORI, THINKING]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
WHY?
[MINORI, THINKING] AKATSUKI...
SHE LIKES HIM.
SHE REALLY LIKES HIM.
AND I...
WHAT DO I DO?
I LIKE HIM, TOO.
(SOBBING)
IT ISN'T FAIR!
SHIROE IS MINE!
NOT FAIR...
I CAN'T SAY THAT.
THAT DOESN'T EVEN MAKE SENSE.
BUT STILL, IT STILL HURTS.
[TOYA] MINORI?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT
HERE ALL BY YOURSELF?
OH. HEY, WHAT'S THE
MATTER WITH YOU?
TOYA...
[TOYA] MINORI, YOU GOT
TO TELL ME WHAT'S UP.
[MINORI] LISTEN, TOYA...
I THINK I'VE GOT A
CRUSH ON MASTER SHIROE.
OH, YEAH. I'M SURE.
[TOYA] SERIOUSLY?
AND YOU JUST NOW
FIGURED THAT OUT?
[MINORI] HUH?
[TOYA] THAT WAS PRETTY
OBVIOUS TO THE REST OF US.
[MINORI] NO WAY!
WELL, WHAT'S NOT TO
LIKE ABOUT HIM?
HE'S A REALLY SMART GUY, AND HE
ACTUALLY CARES ABOUT ALL OF US.
I COULD SEE YOU
LIKING HIM A LOT.
[MINORI] DIDN'T I
KEEP IT TO MYSELF?
[TOYA] NOT LIKE YOU CAN KEEP
ANYTHING FROM YOUR TWIN BROTHER.
I KIND OF THINK MASTER SHIROE'S
PRETTY COOL, TOO, YOU KNOW?
[MINORI] HUH? TOYA!
YOU LIKE HIM, TOO?!
[MINORI] AHH!
[TOYA] NO WAY!
[MINORI] THIS IS
A PROBLEM.
[TOYA] WHY?
[MINORI] WHAT DO
YOU MEAN, WHY?
[TOYA] I DON'T THINK
IT'S A PROBLEM.
[MINORI] HUH?
IT'S ONLY A CRUSH, RIGHT?
THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
[MINORI]
I'M NOT SO SURE.
[TOYA] IT WON'T HURT
FOREVER. I PROMISE.
[MINORI] HMM.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S NATURAL, RIGHT?
IT'S SUPPOSED
TO HURT.
I HAVEN'T LOST ANYTHING.
I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
I GUESS I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO BE ASHAMED OF, DO I?
[TOYA] EXACTLY.
[MINORI] YEAH!
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
THE GIRL SIMPLY ADMIRED HIM.
SHE WANTED TO
BE LIKE HIM...
TO FOLLOW HIM.
TO STAND BEHIND HIM.
THAT WAS ALL.
BUT IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG FOR
THOSE FEELINGS TO GROW DEEPER.
MINORI IS IN LOVE
WITH SHIROE,
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] WE WILL
CHANGE THE WORLD.