[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IN ELDER TALES, A QUEST
IS A TYPE OF MISSION.
THERE ARE MANY TYPES,
RANGING FROM
SIMPLY FINDING MISSING PERSONS
TO GRAND ADVENTURES,
EACH WITH ITS OWN UNIQUE REWARD‐
EXPERIENCE, GOLD
AND OTHER ITEMS,
PLUS MAGICAL KNOWLEDGE
AND CRAFTING RECIPES.
(FLUTES BLOWING)
OUR GRIFFIN‐SUMMONING
FLUTES HAPPEN TO BE
ONE OF THE COMPLETION
REWARDS FOR A HUGE QUEST.
[KARASHIN] HMM.
OK. WE NEED TO GO
ON A SUPPLY RUN HERE.
WE'RE A LITTLE UNDERSTOCKED
AT THE MOMENT.
[TARO] YOU KNOW, EVER
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE,
THERE AREN'T A LOT
OF FOLKS OR GUILDS
WHO WANT TO FIGHT
FOR INGREDIENTS
LIKE THEY USED TO.
FIGHTING IN YOUR
OWN BODY IS PRETTY
SCARY NOWADAYS.
IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU CAN DIE,
BUT I CAN
SEE WHY THEY'RE
TAKING UP CRAFTING
AND MAKING IT
HARD FOR US TO
FILL THE WAREHOUSE.
[KARASHIN] THE LARGER GUILDS
ARE ALWAYS GONNA HAVE
THE BUYING POWER.
[TARO] THE RODERICK MERCHANT
GUILD AND MARINE AGENCY
HAVE ASSIMILATED A LOT OF
THE SMALLER MERCHANT
GUILDS RECENTLY.
[KARASHIN] AND, OF COURSE,
WE CAN'T EXACTLY SIT
ON OUR LAURELS,
EVEN IF WE'RE THE NUMBER 3
CRAFTING GUILD.
WE GOT TO TAKE FULL
ADVANTAGE OF THIS CHANCE
WHILE IT'S STILL
WITHIN OUR REACH.
[TARO] "CHANCE"?
[KARASHIN] MM‐HMM.
AH...
[AKATSUKI] RRGH...
UH! LET ME GO!
SERIOUSLY, I DON'T
HAVE TIME TO BE YOUR
LITTLE PLAYTHING,
AND THAT'S FINAL.
[MARIELLE] YOU LOOK
SO RELAXED, HENRIETTA.
MY HEART'S BEATING
SO FAST.
I'M NOT RELAXED AT ALL,
AND THAT'S WHY I'M
TRYING TO CALM MYSELF BY
SNUGGLING MY AKATSUKI.
I AM NOT YOUR
RELAXATION THERAPY‐
I'M GOING INTO BATTLE
SOON, HONEY PIE,
AND I NEED YOU TO HELP
ME STAY STRONG.
[BOTH] HM...
(DOOR OPENS)
[KARASHIN] HEY, SORRY
I KEPT YOU WAITING.
I MUST HAVE SCREWED UP
PRETTY BAD, MARIELLE.
YOU LOOK KIND OF
UPSET RIGHT NOW.
OH, YOU'RE SO SILLY.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE,
HASN'T IT, KARASHIN?
I UNDERSTAND THAT
YOU AND MARIELLE
HAVE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR QUITE SOME TIME.
[KARASHIN] WE WENT ON A
COUPLE OF HUNTS TOGETHER
WHEN WE STARTED PLAYING,
BUT THEN YOU
STARTED YOUR THING,
AND I WAS DOING MY STUFF,
AND WE JUST GOT TOO BUSY, RIGHT?
[MARIELLE] WE BOTH STARTED
GUILDS, DIDN'T WE?
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO
BE DOING WELL WITH
OVER 700 MEMBERS.
YOU TOTALLY HAVE
US BEAT THAT WAY.
OH, COME ON.
THERE ARE MERCHANTS GUILDS OUT
THERE A LOT BIGGER THAN MINE‐
MARINE AGENCY AND RODERICK.
SO WHY DID YOU
WANT TO MEET ME?
I'M ALL EARS, OF COURSE.
[MARIELLE, THINKING]
AH, HE'S ALREADY GOT
HIS GAME FACE ON...
UH, AHEM, I'D LIKE YOUR HELP
WITH INGREDIENT STOCKS,
SPICES AND WHATNOT
FOR THE CRESCENT BURGER.
KIND OF LIKE THE
WHOLE REAL‐WORLD
DISTRIBUTION‐CHANNEL THING.
SPECIFICALLY, WE NEED
YOUNG DEER MEAT, LETTUCE,
TOMATOES, FLOUR, POTATOES...
[KARASHIN, THINKING] LOOKS LIKE
SHE NEEDS A BIGGER SUPPLY CHAIN
FOR HER RESTAURANT.
ONCE YOU EAT AT CRESCENT MOON,
YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH
HOOKED ON IT FOR LIFE
ON FLAVOR ALONE.
MAN, I NEED TO
GET IN ON THIS.
YOU NEED A
SUPPLY CHAIN.
WHAT PRICE POINT
ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
(TEARING PAPER)
(WHIRRING)
'K. LET ME
THINK ABOUT IT.
THE GUILD COULD
ACTUALLY TURN OUT
A PRETTY TIDY
PROFIT ON THIS.
HOWEVER...
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
IT'S ACTUALLY A PRETTY
GOOD DEAL FOR THEM.
THAT MIGHT BE, BUT YOU KNOW
HE ISN'T GOING TO JUST ROLL OVER
FOR THE FIRST THING
YOU PUT IN FRONT OF HIM.
[MARIELLE, THINKING] OH, YEAH.
HE'S GONNA TRY AND GET A BETTER
DEAL FOR HIMSELF AND HIS GUILD.
[KARASHIN] SO ANYWAY,
I WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT ALL OF THIS IS GOING
INTO OPERATING YOUR
RESTAURANT, CORRECT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
[KARASHIN] RUMOR HAS IT
YOU'RE DOING PRETTY WELL.
THAT'S NICE TO HEAR.
[MARIELLE] GOODNESS KNOWS OUR
CHEFS ARE REALLY PLEASED
WITH THE FEEDBACK
THEY'RE GETTING.
YOU GOT TO TELL ME,
MARIELLE, IS IT A
NEW RECIPE, OR WHAT?
[MARIELLE]
NO. OUR CHEFS ARE
JUST THAT GOOD. HA HA!
THAT'S WHAT I WAS SUPPOSED
TO SAY, WASN'T IT, SHIROE?
SERIOUSLY, I THINK
I'M GONNA CRACK HERE.
[SHIROE]
LISTEN TO ME.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YOU JUST NEED TO
KEEP ON SMILING.
[MARIELLE] "SMILING"?
THAT'S RIGHT. IT'S THE MOST
IMPORTANT THING FOR YOU.
AS LONG AS YOU KEEP
ON SMILING, MARIELLE,
YOUR PARTNER WILL
HANDLE THE REST.
[HENRIETTA]
MM‐HMM.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
MAYBE, BUT SHE LOOKS
LIKE SHE NEEDS
SOMEONE TO THROW HER
A LIFE PRESERVER.
[KARASHIN] I'M DEFINITELY
GONNA GIVE THIS DEAL
SOME SERIOUS CONSIDERATION, BUT
THINK ABOUT THIS FOR A MINUTE.
A DIRECT PARTNERSHIP
BETWEEN SHOPPING STREET 8
AND CRESCENT MOON WOULD
REALLY GROW YOUR BUSINESS.
THE POSSIBILITIES ARE‐
[HENRIETTA] SORRY TO
INTERRUPT, MR. KARASHIN,
BUT IT'S TIME FOR THE
NEXT PART OF THE MEETING.
[KARASHIN] NEXT PART?
[HENRIETTA] MM‐HMM.
THE REST OF OUR GUESTS
SHOULD BE HERE
IN SHORT ORDER.
[MARIELLE]
I'M SORRY.
SINCE WE ALREADY,
LIKE, KNOW EACH OTHER,
I HAD YOU COME IN
A LITTLE EARLY.
[MARIELLE] BUT HENRIETTA SAYS WE
SHOULD NEGOTIATE THIS FAIRLY.
SO WHAT DOES
ALL THIS MEAN?
THE MARINE AGENCY AND
THE RODERICK MERCHANT GUILD
WILL BE COMING TO JOIN
OUR LITTLE MEETING.
WE HAVE OTHER
THINGS TO DISCUSS.
[KARASHIN]
WAIT. WHAT OTHER THINGS
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[MARIELLE]
WE'RE LOOKING
FOR INVESTORS.
WE'RE, LIKE, WANTING
TO EXPAND OUR
BUSINESS INTERESTS.
AAH...
WE SHOULD
TOTALLY ASK
KARASHIN TO STAY!
WE NEED A SECURE
DISTRIBUTION CHANNEL
FOR OUR INGREDIENTS.
OTHERWISE, THIS DOESN'T
STAND A CHANCE OF WORKING.
HEY, WAIT A SECOND!
I MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE SOMETHING
TO ADD TO THAT DISCUSSION.
WHAT KIND OF INVESTMENT
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
WHAT I MEAN IS‐
WE'VE ALREADY LET YOU IN
ON THE FIRST PART OF OUR
DISCUSSION, MR. KARASHIN.
THE REST OF THIS
DIALOGUE MIGHT ALSO
HAVE VALUE TO YOU.
[KARASHIN]
OH, I TOTALLY AGREE.
LET'S JUST FINALIZE
THE TERMS I ALREADY
DISCUSSED WITH YOU.
WE'LL GET ANYTHING
YOU WANT IN ANY
BULK YOU WANT,
AND WE'LL LOCK IT IN
AT THIS RATE, OK?
(WHIRRING)
HMM. 30,000.
30,000?! OK, OK.
ON BEHALF OF THE
SHOPPING STREET 8,
I ACCEPT THE TERMS
OF YOUR DEAL.
[MARIELLE] THAT'S GREAT!
COME ON, HENRIETTA.
WE CAN, LIKE,
LET HIM STAY FOR THE
INVESTOR MEETING, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
THAT'S PERFECTLY FINE.
[MARIELLE] HEE HEE HEE!
[KARASHIN]
HEH HEH HEH...
[MAN]
OK. LET'S SEE. WHAT'S YOUR
TAILORING LEVEL AT NOW?
[MINORI] LEVEL 32.
[MAN] THEN YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO MAKE LEVEL‐30 LEATHER ARMOR.
STICK TO LEATHER APRONS TODAY
AND RAISE YOUR LEVEL SOME MORE.
[MINORI] YES, SIR.
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
SINCE THEN, SHIROE HAS
CONTACTED ME QUITE OFTEN.
HE'S GOT A LOT OF
FRIENDS, AND WE'RE
HERE IN THE SAME WORLD.
THIS SAME MAKE‐BELIEVE
WORLD COME TO LIFE.
WE'RE IN THE SAME PLACE,
BUT THE ONE I'M IN
IS A DREAM THAT'S TURNED
INTO A NIGHTMARE.
[SMASH] RRGH! WHAT THE
HELL IS GOING ON?!
[TOYA]
MINORI, YOU MADE IT OK.
[MINORI] WHAT DO YOU THINK'S
HAPPENED TO US, TOYA?
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER] THAT DAY,
THE DAY REALITY AND ELDER TALES
SWITCHED PLACES...
[TOYA] (PANTING)
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
ALL I COULD DO WAS CRY
AND PRAY THAT SOMEONE
WOULD SWOOP IN AND GET
ME OUT OF THIS MESS.
[TOYA] HUH?
[MINORI] (CRYING)
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER] TOYA WAS
ALREADY STARTING TO ACCEPT IT.
WALKING AROUND ALL OVER
THE PLACE AND RUNNING.
I CAN'T BLAME HIM.
RUNNING WAS NEW FOR HIM,
A BRAND‐NEW EXPERIENCE.
[TOYA]
CHECK IT OUT, MINORI.
HEY, LOOK AT THIS!
I GUESS WE STILL GET
THESE THINGS.
IS THAT COOL, OR WHAT?
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
IT TURNS OUT, WE WERE STILL
GETTING OUR EXP POTIONS
FROM THE SYSTEM
AS A BEGINNER BONUS.
AND, OF COURSE, TOYA WASN'T
GOING TO JUST SIT AND WAIT
WHEN HE HAD A CHANCE
TO DRINK THE HOLY WATER
AND TEST IN A FIGHT
OF SOME KIND.
AND WHEN YOUR LITTLE BROTHER
SHOWS YOU THAT KIND
OF ENTHUSIASM IN A PLACE
YOU'VE NEVER BEEN BEFORE,
YOU START FOLLOWING
HIM REGARDLESS.
BUT THEN...
[SMASH] THEY'RE ON YOUR 4, MAN.
DON'T LET THEM GET AWAY!
[MINORI] HUH! WHA‐? OOH! UH!
MINORI! UH!
(SLAM)
[MINORI] UH! TOYA!
[SMASH] I TOLD YOU,
ALL YOU HAD TO DO TO LIVE
WAS DROP EVERYTHING
IN YOUR INVENTORY.
MAN, IT ALL SEEMS SO REAL,
IT DOESN'T EVEN FEEL
LIKE A VIRTUAL SIMULATION.
WELL, A GAME'S A GAME.
DON'T TAKE IT PERSONAL.
[TOYA]
YOU. WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?!
(SLAM)
[MINORI] OH...
I'M ALIVE?
OH...
[TOYA] MINORI!
[MINORI] TOYA.
(RAIN FALLING)
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
SHIROE TOLD US THAT IF YOU
HAVE SOMETHING THAT MATTERS,
KEEP IT IN THE BANK.
HIS WARNING DIDN'T REALLY
MAKE A WHOLE LOT OF SENSE
UNTIL AFTER WE'D
ALREADY LOST EVERYTHING.
BUT BY THEN, WE JUST
WANTED SOMEONE TO HELP,
ANYONE, NO MATTER
WHO IT WAS...
[SHRADER] WHAT'S
WRONG WITH YOU TWO,
COUPLE OF NUBES IN TOWN?
AIN'T YOU GOT ANY FRIENDS?
IT CAN BE DANGEROUS
OUT HERE, YOU KNOW?
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
SO WHEN HE SHOWED UP,
WE THOUGHT WE'D FOUND A
WAY OUT OF OUR TROUBLE.
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
SHIROE ALWAYS HAD THE POWER
TO MAKE IT IN THIS WORLD.
HE DIDN'T NEED ANYBODY ELSE.
ME? ALL I COULD DO WAS CRY
MYSELF TO SLEEP EVERY NIGHT
BECAUSE I COULDN'T
HACK IT ON MY OWN.
SO WHAT'S CHANGED?
I MEAN, THAT'S WHY I
LOST EVERYTHING IN THE
FIRST PLACE, RIGHT?
ANYWAY, THAT'S THE REASON
I THINK SHIROE SHOULD
JUST LEAVE US HERE
AND NOT EVEN BOTHER
WITH RESCUING US.
SOME BIG SISTER I AM.
(WHIMPERING)
[MICHITAKA] WELL,
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
A COUPLE OF LOST LADIES,
AND THE SO‐CALLED MASTERMIND
BEHIND SHOPPING STREET 8.
[RODERICK] HMM.
HELLO THERE.
I'M MARIELLE, THE GUILD
MASTER OF CRESCENT MOON,
AND HENRIETTA OVER HERE
IS MY HEAD CLERK.
HANG ON THERE.
[HENRIETTA]
MARIELLE, I AM MUCH MORE THAN
A CLERK, AND YOU KNOW IT.
IT'S TRULY A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU, GENTLEMEN.
MY NAME IS HENRIETTA.
WHAT SHE MEANT TO SAY IS
THAT I'M OUR TREASURER.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
NOW THEN, THE MASTER OF THE
MARINE AGENCY, MICHITAKA.
AND RODERICK, MASTER OF
THE RODERICK MERCHANT GUILD.
I HAVE TO NEGOTIATE
THE PROPER AGREEMENT
WITH THESE TWO,
OR WE'RE SUNK.
THIS IS MY BATTLE.
IF I FALL BACK OR FAIL HERE,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO
FACE THE OTHERS.
I MUST MAKE THIS WORK.
[HENRIETTA] NOW, BEFORE WE
GET DOWN TO BUSINESS,
YOU'RE PROBABLY A LITTLE
CURIOUS AS TO WHY WE INVITED
SHOPPING STREET 8
TO JOIN US HERE FIRST.
WE'VE ASKED KARASHIN'S GUILD
TO PROVIDE A SUPPLY CHAIN
OF INGREDIENTS FOR US.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU HAVEN'T DONE A DEAL WITH
THIS GEEK ALREADY, HAVE YOU?!
NO. THERE WOULDN'T
BE A REASON TO CALL US
IF SHE ALREADY FINALIZED
A DEAL WITH HIM.
[RODERICK] WE'RE HERE
FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING] WELL NOW,
MICHITAKA IS A RESPECTED LEADER,
BUT HE ISN'T EXACTLY WHAT
I WOULD REFER TO AS SUBTLE.
RODERICK IS A LOT
LIKE SHIROE, I SUPPOSE,
BUT HE DOESN'T HAVE
ANY OF SHIROE'S CHUTZPAH
OR JOIE DE VIVRE.
OF COURSE WE HAD SOMETHING
ELSE IN MIND, GENTLEMEN.
I THINK YOU'LL FIND
IT'S A PROPOSAL THAT'S
MORE THAN WORTH THE TIME
YOU'RE SPENDING,
AND WE'D LIKE TO OFFER IT TO
BOTH OF YOU WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
HMM.
[SHIROE] THE ONLY THING WE CAN
SELL THAT'LL GIVE US THE MONEY
WE NEED TO RAISE IS OUR NEW
METHOD OF FOOD PREPARATION.
THAT'S REALLY
ALL THERE IS.
[MARIELLE]
OK, BUT ISN'T THAT...
[SHIROE]
PRECARIOUS.
THAT'S WHY WE COULDN'T SELL
CRESCENT BURGERS FOREVER.
SOMEONE'S BOUND TO
STUMBLE ON THIS NEXT.
THAT'S WHY IT'S IMPERATIVE
WE MOVE QUICKLY
AND WE DON'T TIP OUR HAND
UNTIL WE'RE DONE NEGOTIATING.
[MARIELLE] LIKE, TOTALLY,
BUT WE JUST CAN'T GO
BARGING IN THERE
AND NOT HAVE SOMETHING
TO GIVE THEM
IN RETURN, CAN WE?
[SHIROE] THAT WOULD BE ONE
PLACE WHERE WE TRULY HAVE
A DISTINCT ADVANTAGE.
ADVANTAGE HOW?
[SHIROE] OUR ADVANTAGE IS
THAT THEY WANT PROFITS
FROM OUR LITTLE BURGER SHOP.
[HENRIETTA] RIGHT. CRESCENT MOON
IS THE BAIT ON THE HOOK,
AND THEY'LL BITE AS LONG
AS THERE'S PROFIT INVOLVED.
[HENRIETTA AND SHIROE]
OF COURSE WE MUST MAINTAIN
THE NEGOTIATING INITIATIVE.
[SHIROE] KNOWLEDGE IS POWER, AND
THIS TIME, WE HAVE THE POWER.
THE POWER TO CHOOSE WHAT WE
REVEAL TO THEM AND HOW MUCH
IS GOING TO BE
THE KEY TO THIS.
HOWEVER, WE CAN'T GO
TELLING ANY LIES, EITHER.
[HENRIETTA]
THAT'S EASY TO SAY WHEN
I'M GOING TO BE HOLDING
A CARROT OUT THERE FOR THEM
TO SNAP AT THE WHOLE TIME.
[SHIROE]
IF WE'RE GONNA COME BACK
TO THIS TABLE IN THE FUTURE,
WE HAVE TO BE TRUSTWORTHY.
MM, I BETTER GET TO SNUGGLE
WITH MY WITTLE, BITTY
AKATSUKI FOR A WHOLE WEEK, OR
THIS WON'T BE WORTH IT AT ALL!
AHEM, THE CRESCENT MOON
ALLIANCE, WITH HELP,
IS EMBARKING ON A
MAJOR OPERATION.
[MICHITAKA]
"MAJOR OPERATION"?
[HENRIETTA] YOU COULD THINK
OF IT AS A CHALLENGE
ON WHAT YOU MIGHT CALL
A VERY GRAND SCALE.
HOWEVER, WE CONSIDERED
ALL THE POSSIBILITIES
AND REALIZED THAT WE
WEREN'T GOING TO DO THIS
WITHOUT ANOTHER GUILD.
OK, SO YOU
NEED OUR HELP.
ALL RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
SO IT'S A QUEST.
[HENRIETTA] HMM.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING] OH, YAY.
THEY'RE NOT GETTING IT.
(MARIELLE GASPS)
[HENRIETTA]
IT'S NOT LIKE LYING
IF THEY'RE BRAIN
DEAD, RIGHT, SHIROE?
SO WHAT KIND OF
ASSISTANCE DO YOU NEED
FROM ALL OF OUR GUILDS?
BEFORE I GIVE YOU
THE PARTICULARS
OF WHAT WE NEED,
I SHOULD PROBABLY
EXPLAIN OUR ORGANIZATION
A LITTLE BIT FIRST.
[MICHITAKA]
YEAH. I'M OPEN TO HEARING
YOUR STRATEGY, ANYWAY.
[RODERICK] INDEED.
[HENRIETTA] YOU MIGHT ALREADY
BE FAMILIAR WITH THE MAN
OVERSEEING OUR
OPERATION, SHIROE.
[MICHITAKA] WHAT?
[KARASHIN] HUH?
THE VILLAIN BEHIND
GLASSES IS INVOLVED?!
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
THE FIRST BITE, LITTLE FISH.
[MARIELLE]
YOU USED GRIFFINS?
[HENRIETTA]
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN YOUR
RAPID ROUND‐TRIP TO SUSUKINO.
[MARIELLE] YOU CAN ONLY GET
SUMMONING FLUTES LIKE THAT
FROM DARN NEAR KILLING YOURSELF!
[HENRIETTA]
I CAN UNDERSTAND THE TEA
PARTY STRATEGIST HAVING ONE.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
THEY ALWAYS WANT REALLY
CHALLENGING QUESTS.
LOOKS LIKE HIS
REPUTATION PRECEDED HIM.
JUST THEIR KNOWING THAT SHIROE
IS LEADING THIS OPERATION
IS GOING TO LEND A LOT
OF WEIGHT TO ANYTHING
I BRING UP WITH
THESE GUYS NOW.
KIND OF MAKES ME
WONDER WHAT HE DID
TO GET CALLED "VILLAIN
IN GLASSES," ANYWAY.
[SHIROE] AH‐CHOO!
[AKATSUKI]
PARDON, MY LORD.
ARE YOU SICK?
OUR BODIES ARE
MADE BY SOFTWARE,
SO I REALLY
DON'T THINK SO.
[HENRIETTA] LET'S MOVE ON TO
THE MATTER AT HAND, SHALL WE?
I'M CERTAIN THAT,
MOVING FORWARD,
KEEPING SURPRISES
TO A MINIMUM WILL HELP.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE NEED
PEOPLE FOR A QUEST.
WHAT WE REALLY
NEED IS CASH.
[MICHITAKA]
YEAH. THAT FIGURES.
[RODERICK]
AND JUST HOW MUCH?
[HENRIETTA] RIGHT NOW,
THE CURRENT FIGURE WE'RE
LOOKING AT IS...
5 MILLION, ALL IN GOLD.
HUH?!
5 MILLION?!
HMM...
[KARASHIN, THINKING]
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
A QUEST OF ANY KIND
THAT COST THAT MUCH
MONEY TO BUY INTO IN
ANY VERSION OF THE GAME.
YOU DON'T SUPPOSE...
IS IT THE NOVASPHERE PIONEERS?
WITH THE EXPANSION
PACK IN PLACE,
IT MAKES SENSE THAT THE
DEVELOPERS CREATED NEW
LEGENDARY‐CLASS QUESTS
FOR ALL OF US WHO
ARE ALREADY AT LEVEL 90.
[KARASHIN, THINKING] CAN YOU
IMAGINE WHAT THE REWARD WOULD BE
FOR FINISHING THIS QUEST?
[HENRIETTA] IT'S GONNA BE
WORTH A LOT OF MONEY
ONCE WE'RE DONE
WITH OUR LITTLE PLAN.
COME TO THE HOOK, LITTLE FISH.
COME TO THE HOOK.
YOU WANT THIS TO
HAPPEN SO BADLY,
I THINK IT'S TIME THAT MY
FRIEND IN THE LIFE PRESERVER
IS READY TO GIVE YOU
THE PIECE DE RESISTANCE.
[MARIELLE] UH?
[MARIELLE] TRY THIS.
IT'S A NEW RECIPE.
IT'S ONE OF OUR NEW SWEET
AND DELECTABLE DESSERTS
MADE FROM THE EGGS
OF THE GIANT ROKE.
IS THIS CUSTARD?
OH, WOW!
[MICHITAKA]
OH, YOU REALLY MADE ALL
OF THIS FROM ROKE EGGS?
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE,
CONSIDERING THAT A ROKE
IS A POWERFUL MONSTER
AT LEVEL 85 OR BETTER.
TO COOK THE EGGS OF A ROKE
AND TURN IT INTO THIS,
YOU'D NEED A PREVIOUSLY
UNKNOWN, LEVEL‐90 RECIPE.
NOW, OF COURSE, WE'RE
PREPARED TO GIVE YOU
SOMETHING IN RETURN
FOR THE MONEY.
ONCE WE'VE BROUGHT OUR
OPERATION TO A CONCLUSION,
WE'LL BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO GIVE ALL 3 OF YOU
THE FULL DETAILS
ABOUT OUR PLAN.
ADDITIONALLY, WE'RE PREPARED
TO HAVE A SCRIBE MAKE COPIES
OF ALL THE COOKBOOKS
WE'RE CURRENTLY USING
AS WELL AS ALL OF THE COOKING
METHODS WE'VE LEARNED
OVER THE COURSE OF OUR
RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT
OF ALL OUR RECIPES.
[MICHITAKA, THINKING]
DOES THAT MEAN...
[RODERICK, THINKING]
... THEY'RE OFFERING
US ALL THE RECIPES
CRESCENT MOON IS USING?
[KARASHIN, THINKING]
THERE REALLY IS
A SPECIAL RECIPE.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
HOOK, LINE, AND SINKER.
NOW IT LOOKS LIKE ALL I NEED
IS TO REEL THESE LITTLE FISH IN.
THROUGH ASSET LIQUIDATION
AND THE PAST FEW DAYS
OF REFRESHMENTS SALES
AT CRESCENT MOON,
WE CURRENTLY HAVE
500,000 OF OUR OWN.
THAT SAID, WE WOULD BE LOATHE
TO ASK ANY ONE GUILD
TO COME UP WITH THE
REMAINING 4 AND A HALF
MILLION ON THEIR OWN
AND MAKE THEM FINANCIALLY
VULNERABLE IN THE PROCESS.
NATURALLY, WE THOUGHT IT
WOULD BE MORE REASONABLE
TO ASK ALL 3 OF YOU FOR
1 AND A HALF MILLION
APIECE. GOOD?
BUT THAT'S LIKE LIQUIDATING
100 PLAYERS' ASSETS.
THE RODERICK MERCHANT
GUILD AGREES TO YOUR
PROPOSAL, MISS MARIELLE.
SAME HERE!
SHOPPING STREET 8
DOES, AS WELL!
[MICHITAKA] OH, YEAH?
MY MARINE AGENCY'LL
PONY UP THE CASH.
AND IF YOU'D LIKE,
WE'D ALSO BE INTERESTED
IN BEING YOUR ONLY
SPONSOR, TOO.
[MARIELLE] (LAUGHS)
[KARASHIN] NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK!
[RODERICK] YOU'RE NOT TAKING
ALL THE PROFIT FOR YOURSELF.
[MARIELLE] GENTLEMEN, LET'S
TAKE IT EASY, FOR ME, PLEASE?
[TOYA] DID YOU HEAR
FROM HIM AGAIN?
[MINORI] HMM?
[TOYA]
FROM BROTHER SHIROE.
[MINORI] SHH.
[TOYA] UH, LISTEN.
I DIDN'T SAY BEFORE,
BUT I SAW HIM OUTSIDE
A COUPLE OF DAYS AGO...
(MINORI GASPS)
[TOYA] BUT, YOU KNOW,
I COULDN'T BRING MYSELF
TO ASK HIM FOR HELP.
[MINORI] WHY NOT?
[TOYA] I DON'T KNOW.
HE WAS SO COOL AND
NICE AND EVERYTHING.
HE'S SUPER SMART.
HE'S JUST AMAZING,
RIGHT? I JUST...
[MINORI] YEAH.
[MINORI, THINKING]
HE'S RIGHT.
BUT WE HAVE NO RIGHT
TO ASK HIM TO GET
US OUT OF THIS.
[TOYA] SO TELL ME, DO YOU
THINK I COULD BE LIKE HIM?
[MINORI] HUH?
[TOYA] I'VE GOT NO BUSINESS
ASKING HIM TO COME SAVE US.
BUT, HEY, WHAT IF I...
WHAT IF I COULD
BE LIKE SHIROE?
[MINORI] UH...
(MARIELLE SIGHS)
[MARIELLE]
THAT'S IT. I'M DONE.
MAGIC'S GONE.
HEALTH IS GONE.
[HENRIETTA]
MY BODY WON'T MOVE!
(DOOR OPENS)
[MARIELLE] HUH?
[HENRIETTA] THAT SMELL.
[HENRIETTA] AKATSUKI!
YOU'RE NOT
SMELLING ME.
THAT'S PROBABLY
THE PIE.
WHEN YOU'RE TIRED,
LADIES, SWEETS
DO THE TRICK.
[NYAN‐TA]
MM, YEAH.
YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST,
AND AFTER ALL YOU WENT
THROUGH, TOO, OH, THANK YOU.
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE KIND OF
ASKED US TO, SO...
[NYAN‐TA] HE SAID YOU'D
PROBABLY BE TIRED WHEN
YOU GOT BACK, AND‐
[HENRIETTA] (GASPS)
HE SAID THAT?
SO WHAT'S SHIROE
DOING, ANYWAY?
WE REALLY NEED
TO LET HIM KNOW.
[NYAN‐TA]
WELL, HE'S ALREADY WORKING
ON OUR NEXT ASSIGNMENT, HMM.
AND I THINK
IT'S SAFE TO SAY,
MASTER SHIROE ALREADY HAS A LOT
OF CONFIDENCE IN YOU, BABE.
[MARIELLE AND HENRIETTA] HA HA!
I SWEAR, IT'S ALMOST
LIKE HE PLANNED
EVERY SINGLE THING ABOUT THIS
DAY DOWN TO THE LAST DETAIL.
YOU SIMPLY CAN'T BEAT
THE VILLAIN IN GLASSES.
[SHIROE] AH‐CHOO!
[ISAAC]
LET'S BREAK IT INTO TEAMS
FOR TONIGHT'S
SPARING MATCH, PEOPLE.
[MAN 1] YES, SIR!
[MAN 2] RIGHT!
[REZARICK] WHAT'S THE
CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
INVITING US TO, ANYWAY, BOSS?
[ISAAC] SOME DOPEY SHINDIG
ABOUT DISCUSSING THE
FUTURE OF AKIHABARA,
WHICH IS TO SAY,
THEY DIDN'T SAY MUCH AT ALL.
THAT GIRL MARIELLE,
SHE TRIED GETTING
THE SMALLER GUILDS TOGETHER,
BUT THAT DIDN'T TURN OUT
SO GREAT FOR
HER, DID IT?
I'M NOT REALLY
CONCERNED ABOUT HER,
BUT THE GUY SHE'S
WORKING WITH, NOW,
THAT BOTHERS ME.
[REZARICK]
YOU MEAN THE GUY WHO STARTED
THE LOG HORIZON GUILD?
[ISAAC]
YEAH, THAT GUY.
THE VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES,
TEA PARTY BOY.
[MISA]
MILORD, DOES THIS MEAN
WE'RE CANCELING THE NEXT RAID?
[KRUSTY]
YES. WE ARE.
IT'S THE SAME DAY,
AND I NEED TO BE THERE.
[MISA]
IS THIS CONFERENCE
REALLY THAT IMPORTANT?
[KRUSTY] THE CONFERENCE DOESN'T
INTEREST ME THAT MUCH...
OH.
BUT THE PEOPLE BEHIND
IT HAVE MY ATTENTION.
[SHIROE]
WE'RE DOING THIS TOMORROW.
I TOLD YOU I WAS
COMING FOR YOU, AND
I'M KEEPING MY PROMISE.
BE READY, OK?
[MINORI, THINKING]
TOYA SAID HE WANTED
TO BE JUST LIKE SHIROE.
HE WANTS TO OPEN NEW
PATHS JUST LIKE HIM.
AND IF TOYA WANTS
TO BE SOMEONE GREAT...
THEN SO DO I.
(MINORI COUGHS ONCE)
[MARIELLE]
OK, SHIROE. YOU'RE UP.
[SHIROE]
YES. MY BATTLEFIELD...
...IS READY.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
12 GUILD MASTERS HAVE COME
TOGETHER AT THE GUILD BUILDING.
THE BATTLE BEGINS AS SHIROE
FIGHTS WITHOUT A WEAPON.
THE NEW PLAYERS TRAPPED
BY HAMELIN, MINORI AND TOYA,
ARE ABOUT TO BEGIN
THEIR FIGHT, AS WELL.
THEY MUST ALL WORK
TOGETHER IN ORDER TO
OPEN THE DOOR OF HOPE.
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.