[TOYA] YUMMY!
[RUDY] MM! DELICIOUS!
I'VE NEVER EATEN
ANYTHING SO GOOD!
(LAUGHS)
[MARIELLE] THE GOBLINS HAVEN'T
SHOWN THEMSELVES YET?
LIKE, MAYBE THEY'RE
NOT GONNA COME AT ALL.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, WELL,
WE STILL CAN'T LET OUR
GUARD DOWN, MARIELLE.
KRUSTY'S FORWARD STRIKE
FORCE SHOULD HAVE REACHED
NARASHINO BY NOW, RIGHT?
[NYANTA] THEY'RE ALREADY
MAKING PLANS TO LAUNCH
A STRIKE AGAINST THE
GOBLINS' LEAD BATTALION.
[NAOTSUGU] WELL, THE OUTCOME
OF THEIR FIGHT COULD VERY
WELL DECIDE OUR FATE HERE.
[MINORI] SERARA?
[SERARA] HUH?
I NEED TO ASK A FAVOR.
GO AHEAD. YOU CAN
OPEN YOUR EYES NOW.
MM. MM? OH!
(STAMPEDING AND ROARING)
[RAYNESHIA] OHH!
[TAKAYAMA] OK, IT'S STARTING.
[RAYNESHIA] UHH.
(GOBLINS GROWLING)
[TAKAYAMA] DIRECT STRIKE TO
THE ENEMY VANGUARD'S CENTER.
MY LORD, THE MAIN ATTACK
FORCE CAN NOW ADVANCE.
(CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
[KRUSTY] YAAH!
HYAH!
(GOBLINS SCREECH)
WAH!
(CLANG)
(GIANTS GROWLING)
REINFORCEMENTS.
THERE ARE TWO
HILL GIANTS.
[TAKAYAMA] HEALERS,
FLANK BOTH SIDES.
START WITH THE
SMALLER SIDE GROUPS.
MAIN FORCE, CONTINUE TO ADVANCE.
[RAYNESHIA] UH.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] KRUSTY...
HE'S REALLY INTO THIS.
[KRUSTY] HYAH!
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
IT'S SCARY.
IT'S STRANGE, THOUGH.
HE SEEMS SO SAD...
SO LONELY.
(RINGING)
[GIRL 1] COME IN...
[GIRL 2] ATTENTION,
RESUPPLY TEAM 5...
[GIRL 1] YOUR ORDERS ARE
TO CONTINUE TO ADVANCE.
[GIRL 2] TIME TO DEPART.
[GIRL 3] ROGER. DEPARTING
[GIRL 4] CONFIRMING
YOUR DEPARTURE.
[GIRL 5] MAINTAIN POSITION
UNTIL FURTHER ORDERS.
(RINGING)
[GIRL 6] GO AHEAD.
[LILIANA] COME IN, HQ.
THIS IS NARASHINO.
WE'VE MADE OUR RENDEZVOUS.
[GIRL 6]
RIGHT. ROGER.
[LILIANA] THE OCYPETE HAS MET UP
WITH THE SECOND AKIHABARA GROUP.
ONCE THEY COMPLETE
SOME MAINTENANCE,
THEY'LL SET OUT FOR CHOSHI.
SEEMS LIKE THE
NETWORK'S UP.
TELEPATHY COMMUNICATION
IS VITAL.
[KARASHIN] EACH SQUAD
HAS A LEADER, AND THE
SQUADS ARE ABLE TO
COMMUNICATE WITH ONE ANOTHER.
PLUS, THEY HAVE A
CONTACT AT HEADQUARTERS
THEY CAN SPEAK WITH AS WELL.
ALL LINES ARE COMPLETELY OPEN.
[SHIROE] THIS SUPPORTS
SMOOTH COMMUNICATION
AMONG ALL THE SQUADS
IN THE FIELD.
[KARASHIN] KRUSTY AND HIS
FORCE ARE KICKING BUTT, TOO.
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING WELL,
DON'T YOU THINK?
[SHIROE] CHOSHI IS
STILL THE PROBLEM.
[KARASHIN]
WHAT'S THE ISSUE?
[SHIROE] IT'S NOT
ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
WE'RE GONNA GET
A VICTORY.
THE PROBLEM'S GONNA
BE AFTER THE FIGHT.
THE GOBLINS ARE SURE TO
SCATTER ALL OVER THE PLACE.
AND THEY'LL PROBABLY HIT EVERY
OCCUPIED VILLAGE IN THEIR WAY.
WHENEVER POSSIBLE,
WE'VE BEEN MAKING SURE
WE SURROUND THEM, BOX THEM IN,
AND CHIP AWAY AT THE EDGES.
HOWEVER, IF WE DON'T
DEDICATE SOME OF OUR FORCES
TO DEFENDING CHOSHI AS WELL...
THEN THEY'RE GONNA END UP
NIPPING AT OUR HEELS INSTEAD.
THAT'S THE
REAL PROBLEM.
HOW DO WE HANDLE
THE ISSUE AT CHOSHI?
YEAH, I GET IT.
SO, WILL YOU NOT
BE PARTICIPATING IN
THE BATTLE, MY LORD?
I WISH. FOR NOW, I HAVE
TO WAIT UNTIL ALL OUR
UNITS ARE IN THE FIELD.
[AKATSUKI] MM. I SEE.
(SQUEAKING)
[ISUZU] WILL YOU
REALLY BE ALL RIGHT?
[RUDY]
HMM? WITH WHAT?
[ISUZU SIGHS)
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
OF COURSE.
I, RUNDELLHAUS CODE,
AM IN PERFECT PHYSICAL SHAPE.
THERE'S NO ONE IN THE WORLD WHO
CAN STOP ME FROM DOING ANYTHING.
[TOYA] ALL RIGHT.
NO ENEMIES IN SIGHT.
[MINORI] I JUST HOPE
THAT THEY'LL STAY THAT
WAY FOR A WHILE.
[TOYA] DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, SIS.
AS LONG AS WE WORK TOGETHER,
THE GOBLINS ARE NO PROBLEM.
[MINORI] UH.
[TOYA] HUH? WHAT'S WRONG?
[MINORI] THERE. WHAT IS THAT?
[TOYA] HM.
[BOTH] UHH!
[MARIELLE] UHH.
[NAOTSUGU] HOLY CRAP.
THAT'S A LOT FREAKIN' MORE
THAN JUST A FEW HUNDRED.
[NYANTA] MORE LIKE 1,000.
[RUDY] IF 1,000 GOBLINS
HIT THAT TOWN ALL AT ONCE...
[MARIELLE, THINKING] THERE'S
NO WAY I CAN JUST LET THESE KIDS
GO RUNNING INTO THE MIDDLE
OF THIS FIGHT AGAIN.
I CAN'T.
[TOYA] MARIELLE!
[MARIELLE] UH?
LET'S TAKE THE
FIGHT TO 'EM AGAIN.
RIGHT. LET'S
DESTROY THEM ALL
BEFORE THEY CAN
REACH THE TOWN!
[MARIELLE] UH...
[SERARA] COME ON, NYANTA!
LET US GO!
[NYANTA] MEOW?
[MARIELLE] UH.
[NAOTSUGU] MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE] MM.
HMM. EVERYBODY'S
READY TO GO.
ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS
JUST GIVE US THE ORDER.
[MARIELLE] UH... MM.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS!
YOU WERE TOTALLY AWESOME
THE LAST TIME YOU DID THIS!
BUT NOW WE NEED, LIKE, ONE
MORE GOOD FIGHT OUT OF YOU.
I BELIEVE IN EVERY SINGLE
ONE OF YOU AND YOU CAN DO
THIS ONE MORE TIME!
EVERYONE, INTO BATTLE!
(ALL CHEERING)
[MINORI] LET'S SPLIT
INTO TEAMS, GUYS.
THAT WAY, WE CAN HANDLE
A SECOND WAVE IF IT HITS US.
TOYA, OUR PARTY IS GONNA
FOCUS ON SUPPORTING
EVERYBODY ELSE'S ATTACK.
[TOYA] OK. GOT IT!
[RUDY]
LEAVE IT TO ME.
MASTER SHIROE!
THE CAMP GROUP IN CHOSHI
HAS JUST MADE CONTACT WITH
THE SAHUAGIN FORCES.
THERE ARE ONLY 60 ADVENTURERS
AND AT LEAST 1,000 SAHUAGIN.
THEY'RE COMPLETELY OVERWHELMED.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO?!
WE'VE GOT TO GET THE
OCYPETE INTO THE FIGHT.
(HORN BLARES)
[FOX‐GIRL] AAH!
[AXE‐WIELDER]
UHH! OOH!
[HOODED ADVENTURER] UHH!
(BOTH GASP) AAH!
[NAOTSUGU] HUH.
[NYANTA] NAOTSUGU‐CHI...
WE HAVE A DUTY TO
EVERYONE TO RECOVER
OUR MAGIC POINTS
SO WE CAN CAST OUR
OWN SPELLS. NYAH?
[SHORYU] ALL RIGHT.
HERE YOU GO. DRINK UP.
[NAOTSUGU] THANKS, HOSS.
(SWALLOWING)
HUH.
(TOYA GRUNTING)
WHIRLWIND SLASH!
[NYANTA] THAT BOY'S REALLY
DONE SOME GROWING, HASN'T HE?
[NAOTSUGU] HE HAS.
I MEAN, HE STILL HAS A WAYS
TO GO TO BE AS AWESOME AS ME,
BUT THE LITTLE DUDE'S
WELL ON HIS WAY.
[NYANTA] SERARA'S GETTING
GOOD, TOO. NYAH.
SHE USED TO ONLY
THINK ABOUT HEALING.
[SERARA] GO GET 'EM, WOLFIE.
(WOLFIE BARKING)
IT LOOKS LIKE NOW SHE'S STARTING
TO USE OFFENSIVE TECHNIQUES,
AND REMEMBERING TO
SUMMON HER COMPANION.
[NYANTA] AND THEM...
THE BARD GIRL AND
THE SORCERER BOY.
THEY'VE IMPROVED, TOO.
[RUDY AND ISUZU] HMM.
START THE DANCE OF PAVANE!
[NYANTA] THEY COMPLEMENT
EACH OTHER NICELY.
JUST LIKE THEY'RE READING
EACH OTHER'S THOUGHTS.
[RUDY] BURNING STRIKE!
(EXPLOSION, FIRE ROARS)
[NAOTSUGU] NOW RUNDELLHAUS IS
LIKE A BIG WALKING PILE OF MOJO.
HE'S PUTTING IT ALL OUT THERE.
HE'S USING ALL HIS PENT‐UP
TEENAGER EMOTIONS IN HIS MAGIC.
[MINORI] RUDY. DON'T BLAST
EVERYTHING SO HARD.
[RUDY] YEAH. I GOT IT.
[MINORI] SERARA.
EVERYONE'S HEALTH IS GOOD.
GET BACK ON OFFENSE!
YOU'LL BE MORE HELP
THERE FOR NOW.
[SERARA] ALL RIGHT.
[MINORI] 10 SECONDS UNTIL WE
CAN RECAST GUARDIAN BARRIER!
[NAOTSUGU] AND MINORI
DOES A GOOD JOB
OF KEEPING A WATCHFUL
EYE ON THE BIG PICTURE
THROUGHOUT THE FIGHT.
EVERYONE'S TEAMWORK,
ENEMY LOCATION,
ENEMY ENCOUNTER ORDER,
AND THE ENEMY DEFEAT ORDER.
[NYANTA] WHAT'S NICE IS THAT
YOU GET TO USE THAT INFORMATION
LATER ON AFTER YOU'VE STARTED
TO KEEP TRACK OF IT.
AND THEN I PUT IT IN A
LITTLE BOOK I CALL "TACTICS."
THAT WAY, IT JUST BECOMES
EASIER NEXT TIME.
ALL THESE FACTS
SHE'S TRACKING
HAS HER FIGHTING
JUST LIKE SHIROE.
DOWN TO THE
PERCENTAGE POINTS,
AND 30 SECONDS AT A TIME.
I THINK...
[NAOTSUGU] I THINK
WHAT HE MEANT WAS
THAT HE WAS FIGHTING BY LOOKING
30 SECONDS INTO THE FUTURE.
AND HE CLOSELY TRACKS HIS
ALLIES' REMAINING MP DOWN TO 1%.
NOW, TRACKING THE MP OF
ALLIES IN DIFFERENT CLASSES
IS IMPOSSIBLE WITHOUT
MONITORING THE STATUS SCREEN.
BUT HE CAN TRACK IT TO
A SINGLE PERCENTAGE POINT.
PLUS, MONITOR THE ENEMY STATUS
TO PREDICT WHERE THE BATTLE
WILL BE IN 30 SECONDS.
HE CAN MAKE EVERYTHING HAPPEN
THE WAY HE WANTS IT TO.
THAT'S WHEN SHIROE
IS AT HIS BEST...
IN HIS OWN CREATED COMBAT.
A FULL CONTROL ENCOUNTER.
[MINORI] TOYA!
YOU NEED TO FALL BACK!
HEY, SERARA, I'M GONNA NEED YOU
TO CAST A GROUP HEALING SPELL!
ROGER THAT!
[NAOTSUGU] OF COURSE, WE
ACTUALLY LIVE WITHIN
THIS WORLD NOW,
[TOYA] EAT THIS!
[NAOTSUGU] SO, I DOUBT
HE'S ABLE TO SEE A FULL 30
SECONDS AHEAD LIKE HE USED TO.
EITHER WAY, MINORI IS DEFINITELY
TRYING TO MIMIC OR RECREATE
HER OWN VERSION OF SHIROE'S
FULL CONTROL ENCOUNTER.
[NYANTA] MINORI‐CHI IS
CHASING AFTER SHIROE,
THAT'S FOR SURE. NYAH.
YEAH. MAKES ME WONDER
HOW FAR AHEAD SHE CAN SEE.
(DISTANT SHRIEKING)
HUH?
UHH!
[NAOTSUGU] DO YOU HEAR THAT?
[NYANTA] IT'S A DRUID
SPECIAL ATTACK MAGIC.
THE SHRIEKER ECHO. HM.
[MINORI] I HAD SERARA SET
IT UP AS A WARNING SYSTEM.
I'M SURE THE GOBLINS
ARE COMING BACK.
[TOYA] WE'VE GOT
THIS ONE, MASTER!
[RUDY] AGAIN?!
[ISUZU] HANG ON, RUDY!
[SERARA] OH, UM, YOU DO
YOUR BEST, TOO, NYANTA! BYE!
[SHORYU] HEY! WAIT, YOU GUYS!
[MINORI] MASTER NAOTSUGU,
[GROUP] HUH?
[MINORI] WE CAN HANDLE
THE GOBLINS IF YOU LET
US GO AFTER THEM NOW.
ISUZU THE BARD IS WITH US,
SO WE SHOULD HAVE GOOD
SUSTAIN ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
WE'LL TAKE CARE
OF THIS, MASTER!
HEY, WAIT! MINORI!
[MINORI] I'LL BE THE OPERATOR!
SERARA, I NEED YOU TO FOCUS
ON HEALING FOR NOW!
[SERARA] BUT WAIT,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE FIELD MONITOR, MINORI!
[MINORI] I'LL HANDLE
MAKING SURE EVERYONE'S
MAGIC POINTS STAY HIGH.
[TOYA] GOBLINS!
(GOBLINS GROWLING)
[MINORI, THINKING]
THAT'S A LOT OF GOBLINS.
WE'VE GOTTA TRY HITTING
THEM ALL AT ONCE.
BUT TOYA, AS A SAMURAI,
ISN'T FAST ENOUGH YET.
RUNDELLHAUS!
I'VE GOT THIS ONE.
I'LL SHOW YOU ALL THE
AMAZING AND MELODIOUS
POWER OF MY MAGIC!
GRAND SERPENTINE LIGHTNING!
(GOBLINS GRUMBLING)
[TOYA] THEY'RE COMING!
[MINORI] ISUZU?
[ISUZU] RIGHT!
CRAWLING OF THE
SNAILS BALLAD!
[TOYA] LET'S DO THIS!
HEAD SPLITTER!
[RUDY] FROST SPEAR!
[SERARA] UH, UH, UHH! DISMISSAL!
ALL RIGHT!
[ISUZU] I GOT
MINE, TOO.
[RUDY] PIECE OF CAKE.
MISS ISUZU, I KNOW
YOU ARE IMPRESSED?
MY MAGIC WAS PRETTY AWESOME
BACK THERE, RIGHT?
(DOG HOWLS)
(ISUZU GIGGLES)
OF COURSE!
YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD
WIDDLE BOY.
[RUDY] WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU MAKING FUN OF ME?
(ISUZU GIGGLES)
I DON'T KNOW. AM I?
[RUDY] WHAT?
[ISUZU] DOWN, BOY.
I'M NOT MAKING FUN OF
YOU AT ALL, RIGHT?
[RUDY] YEAH?
[MINORI, THINKING] I CAN
ONLY SEE 5 SECONDS AHEAD,
AND ONLY 5% AT A TIME.
I CAN DO 10 SECONDS
ONCE IN A WHILE,
BUT I'M NOWHERE NEAR SHIROE YET.
(SQUEALING)
HUH?
[TOYA] THAT'S REALLY
CLOSE TO THE TOWN.
WE GOTTA GO!
(GIRL GROANING)
(CHIME)
[MARIELLE] HM? SHIROE?
YOU'VE GOT AN HOUR UNTIL
THE OCYPETE GETS OVER TO YOU.
[SHIROE] HOLD OUT
A LITTLE LONGER.
OK, YOU GUYS.
WE'VE GOT AN HOUR UNTIL OUR
REINFORCEMENTS GET HERE.
KEEP ON FIGHTING! GO!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(TOYA PANTING)
(ALL PANTING)
[ISUZU] RUDY!
I'M GONNA BE FINE.
[ISUZU, THINKING] HIS MAGIC
POINTS ARE ALMOST GONE.
HOW LONG DO WE HAVE
TO KEEP THIS UP?
[MINORI] HEY, GUYS?
[ISUZU] UHH.
[MINORI]
MARIELLE JUST CALLED ME.
THERE'S A SHIP WITH
REINFORCEMENTS ON THE WAY
AND IT'LL BE HERE PRETTY SOON.
THEY'LL SEND US HELP AS SOON
AS THEY PULL INTO PORT, OK?
[SERARA] REALLY?
[TOYA] THAT'S AWESOME NEWS!
LET'S KEEP IT UP!
[ISUZU] GOOD. I WAS
GETTING WORRIED.
[TOYA] I'VE GOTTA EAT!
(THUNDER)
[MINORI] RAIN?
(HOWLING)
(MINORI GASPS)
(THUNDER)
[TOYA] A DIRE WOLF!
[RUDY] AND HE BROUGHT
HIS FRIENDS WITH HIM.
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(TOYA GRUNTING)
[TOYA] AH! HYAH!
[ISUZU] UHH. UHH!
(WOLF GROWLING)
[BOTH] AH!
[SERARA] WILLOW SPIRITS, GO!
(WOLF GROWLING)
[TOYA] UHH!
[MINORI] FOUR QUARTERS,
MEDITATION!
[SERARA] PLEASE STOP!
[MINORI] SERARA!
JUST STAY FOCUSED
ON THE DIRE WOLF!
[SERARA] BUT THEN I WON'T
BE ABLE TO HEAL ANYONE.
[MINORI] I'LL TAKE OVER
THE HEALING FOR NOW, OK?
[MINORI, THINKING]
TWO DIRE WOLVES AND
THE HOBGOBLINS.
TOYA DOESN'T STAND A
CHANCE IF THEY RUSH HIM.
TOYA! YOU TAKE THE
HOBGOBLINS AND ONE
OF THE DIRE WOLVES!
RUDY! ISUZU! FOUR QUARTERS
HAS ANOTHER 32 SECONDS!
ATTACK BEFORE IT RUNS OUT!
[RUDY] OK.
[ISUZU] ROGER!
[SHIROE] WHEN YOU ENCOUNTER
A DIFFICULT OPPONENT,
THERE ARE A NUMBER
OF DIFFERENT STRATEGIES.
TAKING OUT THE WEAKER
ENEMIES IS ONE STRATEGY.
BY LOWERING THE NUMBER
OF POTENTIAL ATTACKERS,
YOU'RE ALSO REDUCING THE AMOUNT
OF DAMAGE THEY CAN DO TO YOU.
[MINORI] AAH!
(GRUNTING)
[RUDY] FRIGID WIND!
[ISUZU] BEAT OF RESONANCE!
[MINORI] UHH. TOYA!
[TOYA] AAH!
(MINORI GASPS)
[TOYA] UHH!
[RUDY]
MISS ISUZU, OVER THERE.
WE'VE GOTTA GET
THE OTHER WOLF!
[ISUZU] YEAH.
(WOLF GROWLING)
[RUDY AND ISUZU] UHH! UHH!
[TOYA] AAH!
(SERARA GASPS)
HERE YOU GO!
[MINORI] THE HEALING
CAN'T KEEP UP!
[MINORI, THINKING] NO. THEY'RE
ALL ATTACKING HIM AT ONCE.
[TOYA] (GRUNTING) AH!
IF HE KEEPS LOSING HIS
HIT POINTS, HE WON'T MAKE IT.
HE'S GOT 9 SECONDS TO LIVE.
I CAN CAST A PURIFICATION
BARRIER IN 8 SECONDS.
NO, NO, NO. A SPELL
LIKE THAT WON'T WORK
AGAINST THESE MONSTERS.
(HEARTBEAT)
[MINORI, THINKING]
IF TOYA LOSES... IF HE LOSES.
(BELL TOLLS)
(GASPS)
[RUDY] YAAAAH!
UHH!
(WOLF GROWLING)
[ISUZU] RUDY!
[TOYA] YOU IDIOT!
[RUDY] HA HA HA! MR. TOYA!
I'LL SHOW THIS LITTLE
PUPPY WHO HIS MASTER IS!
STOP IT! ARE YOU INSANE?!
[RUDY] HA HA HA!
[ISUZU] UHH!
[RUDY] I'VE GOT THIS,
MISS ISUZU!
THESE MUTTS AREN'T GONNA
GET THE BETTER OF ME!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(GROANING)
[ISUZU] NO!
[TOYA] RUDY!
(RUNDELLHAUS GRUNTING)
DON'T YOU KNOW WHO I AM?
I AM RUNDELLHAUS CODE!
THE ADVENTURER!
(GRUNTING)
[MINORI] RUDY!
[TOYA] RUDY!
[MINORI] I CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING!
[SERARA] I'LL DO IT.
NATURE REVIVE!
UHH. THE REVIVAL
SPELL ISN'T WORKING!
[TOYA] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THEN TRY ANOTHER ONE, MINORI!
[MINORI] HMM.
PRAYER TO THE SOUL CALL!
[SERARA] THAT ISN'T
WORKING, EITHER.
[TOYA] WELL, COME ON!
(ISUZU GASPING)
[ISUZU] I'M SORRY...
IT'S NOT WORKING BECAUSE...
RUDY IS...
AN NPC.
(ALL GASP)
[ISUZU] HE JOINED
US IN OUR PARTY
AND WENT ON ADVENTURES WITH US.
ATE WITH US.
BUT HE'S NOT ONE OF US.
[ISUZU]
AND YOU'RE IN. UH, OK.
(BEEPING)
[ISUZU] WELL, THAT'S WEIRD.
ARE YOU ONE OF THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND?!
[RUDY] DO YOU THINK
WE COULD MAYBE NOT SHARE
THIS WITH EVERYONE ELSE?
[ISUZU] YEAH, BUT RUDY...
ISUZU, I'M GONNA
BECOME AN ADVENTURER.
OH.
[ISUZU] THAT'S WHY
HE DID SO MUCH.
WHY HE WORKED SO HARD.
HE WORKED SO HARD
TO PROVE HIMSELF.
(CRYING)
I COULDN'T BE THE ONE
WHO WAS GONNA STOP HIM.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
[TOYA] NO WAY. RUDY'S ONE
OF THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND?
WE'VE GOTTA
SAVE HIM! SOMEHOW!
YOU'VE GOTTA TRY ANOTHER
REVIVAL SPELL, SERARA!
I CAN'T. IT'S STILL
ON COOLDOWN.
(GASPS)
MAYBE A HEALING SPELL.
UHH.
[ISUZU] HUH?
[SERARA] WHEN I DO IT,
IT FEELS LIKE I'M GETTING
AT LEAST A SMALL RESPONSE.
(ISUZU GASPS)
[SERARA] BUT I'M SORRY IF
REVIVING HIM DOESN'T WORK.
(GASPS)
THERE'S HOPE!
[ALL] HUH?
[MINORI] WE NEED YOUR
HELP, SHIROE! SHIROE!
[SHIROE] UHH.
[MINORI] SHIROE,
HELP US, PLEASE!
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
RUNDELLHAUS IS DEAD.
HE WAS ONE OF THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
AND THE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND CANNOT REVIVE.
THAT IS THE LAW OF THIS WORLD.
BUT TO GRANT MINORI'S WISH,
SHIROE CHALLENGES THE LAWS.
FOR A TRUE FRIEND WHO WOULD
TRAVEL THE WORLD WITH YOU
TO FIND A DAWN THAT
NO ONE HAS EVER SEEN.
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] WE WILL
CHANGE THE WORLD.