[TOYA] HMM.
[MINORI] HEY. ARE WE
REALLY GONNA... TOYA?
[TOYA] HMM.
[MARIELLE] OH WOW!
AHH!
TAKOYAKI! AHH!
[HENRIETTA] YOU CAN EAT LATER.
WE STILL HAVE THINGS TO BUY.
OH, WHY ARE YOU
SO MEAN, UMEKO?
[HENRIETTA] ERR!
YOU PROMISED NOT TO CALL
ME BY THAT NAME AGAIN.
NOW LET'S GO.
AAH!
(WHIMPERING)
OHH?
HUH.
[HENRIETTA]
WHAT'S WRONG?
HOLY MOLY!
AKIHABARA REALLY HAS
CHANGED, YOU KNOW?
HMM.
[HENRIETTA]
IT'S BEEN A WEEK.
REAL CHANGE
TAKES A WHILE.
I'D LIKE TO BELIEVE
IT'S GOING TO STICK,
BUT LET'S JUST TEMPER
OUR OPTIMISM A LITTLE.
(SLAM)
[ISAAC] YOU GOT OUR ATTENTION
NOW, SO WHY DON'T YOU TELL US
WHAT YOU AND THAT RINKY‐DINK
GUILD OF YOURS HAS IN MIND?
OR WAIT! DO YOU
EVEN KNOW THAT YET?
[SHIROE] I HAVE TWO PRIMARY
GOALS FOR THE ROUND TABLE.
WE HAVE TO START BY MAKING
THE SOCIAL CLIMATE LIVABLE
FOR THE PEOPLE
HERE IN AKIHABARA.
PART OF THAT IS COMMERCE
LIKE THE CRESCENT
BURGER PHENOMENON.
MARIELLE.
I'M SURE YOU'RE ALL AWARE
THAT MY GUILD IS CURRENTLY
RUNNING A FAST FOOD
RESTAURANT CALLED
CRESCENT MOON...
COME ON, MARIELLE.
YOU CAN DO IT.
[MARIELLE] IT'S BECAUSE WE
PREPARE FOOD WITH ACTUAL FLAVOR,
AND IT'S TIME WE REVEALED
THAT SECRET TO YOU.
OH!
SO HERE'S THE TRICK.
GET NORMAL INGREDIENTS TOGETHER,
DON'T USE THE COMMAND
MENU TO PREPARE THEM.
PLUS, A CHEF HAS TO DO IT,
AS IN SOMEONE WITH
THE SUBCLASS OF CHEF
WHO DOES IT HIMSELF.
HUH?
[MARIELLE] ALSO, DON'T
EXPECT MUCH FROM A CHEF
WITH A LOW SKILL LEVEL.
THAT'S IT REALLY.
THE TRICK TO MAKING A BETTER
BURGER IS THAT THERE ISN'T ONE.
SO YOU JUST COOK YOUR MEALS
YOURSELF INSTEAD OF USING
THE COMMAND MENU
TO DO IT FOR YOU?
WELL, THAT'S NOT
MUCH OF A SECRET.
[SHIROE] THIS DISCOVERY
IS THE FIRST OF ITS KIND,
BUT IT'S NOT THE ONLY ONE.
THE FACT THAT WE CAN MAKE
CHANGES LIKE THIS IN THIS
WORLD IS FAR TO
SERIOUS TO IGNORE.
MICHITAKA...
[MICHITAKA]
YEAH. THE MARINE AGENCY,
WITH SOME HELP FROM RODERICK'S
MERCHANT GUILD AND THE PEOPLE
FROM SHOPPING STREET 8,
WE'VE ACTUALLY CREATED
A WORKING STEAM ENGINE.
[OTHERS] OHH!
TECHNICALLY,
IT'S NOTHING MORE
THAN A PROTOTYPE.
WE STILL HAVE A
FEW BUGS TO WORK OUT,
BUT IT'S PRETTY
GOOD AS PROOF
OF CONCEPTS GO.
[SHIROE]
IT'S STILL PRETTY
IMPRESSIVE THAT YOU WENT
AND DID THAT IN
JUST 12 HOURS.
UGH. HANG ON. WHAT'S
THE POINT IN TELLING
US ALL ABOUT THAT?
BASICALLY, IT MEANS THE
SECRET YOU JUST LEARNED
ABOUT COOKING ACTUALLY
APPLIES TO ANY OTHER
SKILL YOU MIGHT POSSESS.
BACK WHEN WE WERE PLAYING,
"ELDER TALES" DIDN'T LET
US USE STEAM ENGINES.
HOWEVER, ANY PLAYER WITH
THE PROPER SKILL LEVEL
AND DETERMINATION ONLY
NEEDS THIS WORLD'S
MATERIALS, A GOOD IDEA, AND
THE POWER OF HIS OWN HANDS.
WE CAN CREATE THINGS THAT
WEREN'T A PART OF THIS WORLD
BEFORE WE ARRIVED HERE.
[RODERICK] AND THAT MEANS
WE'RE AT THE START OF
A TECHNOLOGICAL REVOLUTION.
AND NEW TECHNOLOGIES
MEAN NEW BUYERS.
[KARASHIN] AND THAT WILL
NECESSITATE AN INCREASE
IN ALL OUR CITIZENS'
SPENDING POWER.
THEY WON'T BE SITTING
AROUND DOING NOTHING.
WITH THIS POTENTIAL,
I THINK I CAN SPEAK FOR
ALL 3 CRAFTING GUILDS.
WE WHOLEHEARTEDLY
RECOGNIZE THE ROUND
TABLE CONFERENCE.
[SERARA] AHH!
AW, YEAH.
THAT'S 3, BABY.
THIS CITY'S DEAD
RIGHT NOW.
EVERYONE'S WALKING
AROUND IN DESPAIR,
AND MOST PEOPLE JUST
DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THEMSELVES.
LIVING IS WAY TOO CHEAP.
I'M TALKING ABOUT
ECONOMIC STIMULUS.
CREATE A SERIES
OF PRODUCTS AND
GOODS THAT ENHANCE
LIVES AND ENCOURAGE
PEOPLE TO SPEND TIME
EARNING MONEY.
[SHIROE]
TO EARN MONEY OR FOSTER
TRADE IN BARTERING,
WE'D NEED A LOT MORE
HUNTING PARTIES.
THIS IN TURN WOULD GIVE
THE WARRIOR GUILDS MORE
WORK AS BODYGUARDS.
PUBLIC SAFETY IS NEXT.
[SHIROE]
IT'S NOT LIKE WE NEED
DRACONIAN LAWS TO DO THIS.
IN FACT, THERE ARE
PLACES WHERE PLAYERS
SHOULD STILL FIGHT.
THE BOUNDARIES
OF HUNTING GROUNDS
FOR EXAMPLE.
WE SHOULDN'T ELIMINATE
THE ESSENCE OF COMPETITION
FROM OUR DAILY LIFE.
WE AGREE ON THAT.
[SHIROE] HOWEVER, THERE ARE
STILL OTHER THINGS THAT
NEED TO BE CONSIDERED OUT
OF BOUNDS... PLAYER KILLINGS.
HUH?
[SHIROE] WE REALLY SHOULD
CONSIDER THE PROHIBITION
OF PLAYER KILLING IN
THE LOWER LEVEL ZONES
OUTSIDE THE CITY.
THERE'S NO POINT IN FIGHTING
ANYONE BELOW LEVEL 50.
WE DON'T NEED
ANY BULLIES.
[SHIROE] LET'S TAKE A LOOK
AT HUMAN RIGHTS NEXT.
WHEN YOU CONSIDER THAT
DEATH IS NO LONGER
AN ABSOLUTE NOW...
I'VE ALREADY
SEEN AN EXAMPLE...
KIDNAPPING AND FALSE
IMPRISONMENT CAN BE WORSE.
AND LEAVING OR JOINING
A GUILD SHOULD BE UP TO
AN INDIVIDUAL AND
NEVER COMPULSORY.
DEFINITELY.
[SHIROE] ALL RIGHT.
THE LAST ITEM.
THE RIGHTS WE DISCUSSED.
WE ARE NOT THE ONLY
ONES WHO NEED THEM.
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
HAVE TO BENEFIT FROM THIS.
[OTHERS] HUH?
HUH?
THIS WORLD MIGHT
LOOK FAMILIAR,
BUT IT'S NOT THE
"ELDER TALES" WE KNEW.
OUR TECHNOLOGICAL
ADVANCES ARE PROOF
THINGS ARE CHANGING.
[RODERICK]
THAT MAY BE TRUE,
BUT DON'T YOU THINK‐
[SHIROE]
"ELDER TALES" IS THE
BASIS FOR ALL THIS,
BUT THIS IS A
DIFFERENT WORLD THAN
THE ONE WE USED TO KNOW.
WE CAN'T JUST ASSUME THAT
EVERY SINGLE FACET'S
GONNA BE THE SAME.
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
ARE THE ORIGINAL RESIDENTS
INSIDE THIS WORLD.
WE'RE THE STRANGERS,
AND WE'RE VASTLY OUTNUMBERED.
SO YOU'RE SAYING THESE
GUYS AREN'T NONPLAYER
CHARACTERS ANYMORE?
THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY'RE ALL
UNIQUE NOW.
THEY HAVE
THEIR OWN DREAMS,
DESIRES, AND GOALS.
THAT IS SO MORONIC.
[SHIROE] HAVE YOU EVER
SPOKEN WITH ANY OF THEM
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE?
WHY THE HELL WOULD I?
[MARIELLE] HEY. UH, CAN
I ADD SOMETHING TO THIS?
I TOTALLY JUST
REMEMBERED SOMETHING.
WE DON'T JUST
SERVE ADVENTURERS.
[KARASHIN] HUH?
THAT'S RIGHT. A LOT OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
WERE COMING BY.
IT'S NOT SURPRISING.
EVERYONE WANTS
A GOOD MEAL!
[SHIROE] A LOT OF THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND CURRENTLY WORK
IN THE MARKET OR
THE GUILD BUILDING.
WE CAN'T GET
BY WITHOUT THEIR
CONTRIBUTION TO SOCIETY.
WE NEED THEM.
HOWEVER, I'M PRETTY
SURE THEY CAN DO
WITHOUT US JUST FINE.
IF WE DON'T GOVERN OURSELVES
AND DO IT SOONER THAN LATER,
WE'RE RUNNING THE RISK OF
A BACKLASH AGAINST US
FROM A GROUP THAT CAN BEAT
US WITH SHEER NUMBERS.
ARE YOU SAYING WE MIGHT END
UP FIGHTING A WAR WITH THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] IF WE'RE THE
LEAST BIT RESPONSIBLE,
THEN WE HAVE TO
CONSIDER IT, YES.
THOSE OF THE D. D. D. AGREE TO
JOIN THE ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE.
WE'LL BE PROACTIVE.
THE BRIGADE OF THE
WEST WIND AGREES, TOO.
YOU USED FULL
CONTROL AND COUNTER.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
NOW, HASN'T IT?
OH, MAN, I WISH
YOU'D JOINED US.
WELL, DIVIDING THE
CITY WOULD BE USELESS.
THE BLACK SWORD
KNIGHTS ARE ALSO IN.
HONESTY AGREES,
AS WELL.
HMM.
GLENDALE'S ON BOARD.
RADIO MARKET AGREES.
US, TOO!
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
TOTALLY AGREES.
[MARIELLE] AND SO THE ROUND
TABLE CONFERENCE WAS
FOUNDED ON THAT DAY,
AND OF COURSE, WE WENT PUBLIC
WITH THE BIG RECIPE SECRET. HA!
[KRUSTY] THE WORLD WE'RE
IN IS OBVIOUSLY NOT THE
"ELDER TALES" WE ONCE KNEW.
WE NEED TO ACCEPT
THIS AND STOP TREATING
IT LIKE A GAME.
WE ADDRESSED HUMAN RIGHTS AND
SECURITY IN OUR FIRST ATTEMPT.
[RODERICK] NEXT ITEM ON OUR
AGENDA IS FINDING OUT MORE
ABOUT WHY THE TRANSPORT
GATES DON'T WORK.
WE'LL DO SOME RESEARCH
ON TIMING THE FAIRY RINGS.
YEAH. WELL, YOU KNOW,
I THINK IT'S ALL GONNA WORK OUT.
[EINS] EACH USE OF THE GUILD
BUILDING WILL COST ONE GOLD.
THIS WILL SERVE AS A
TAX FOR INFRASTRUCTURE.
HMM.
[MICHITAKA] EAT, DRINK,
ENJOY ALL THE NEW FLAVORS
TO YOUR HEART'S CONTENT!
[KARASHIN] GO AHEAD
AND EAT UP, EVERYONE!
[SMASH]
HEY! THAT'S MINE!
[LYCOPENE] OH, I
DON'T THINK SO.
[MARIELLE] OH, AND HAMELIN,
THEY WENT AND DISBANDED.
HMM.
[HENRIETTA]
TRUE TO HIS WORD,
SHIROE ACTUALLY
DENIED THEIR ACCESS
TO THE GUILD BUILDING.
[MARIELLE]
SO FOR A WHILE, THEY WERE
LOCKED IN THEIR GUILD HALL.
[HENRIETTA] RIGHT! AND IT DID
NOT MAKE THEM VERY HAPPY.
NOW A FEW OF THEM DID
THE SMART THING AND USED
THE CALL OF HOME TO TELEPORT
BACK OUTSIDE THE CITY GATES
AND DIDN'T BOTHER TRYING TO
GET BACK INTO THE BUILDING.
AND SOME OF THE NOT‐SO‐SMART
ONES JUST WENT
AND KILLED THEMSELVES SO
THEY'D HAVE THEIR OWN
RETURN POINT IN THE CATHEDRAL.
[MARIELLE] REGARDLESS,
THEY CAN'T USE THIS
GUILD BUILDING ANYMORE.
[HENRIETTA] EVERY LAST HAMELIN
MEMBER REALLY LEFT THE CITY.
YEAH. THAT'S NICE.
[HENRIETTA] HMM?
[MARIELLE]
WELL, AS YOU KNOW,
ALL THE KIDS WHO RAN
AWAY FROM HAMELIN THAT
DAY WANTED TO JOIN US.
SO WE HAD TO MOVE INTO A LARGER
GUILD HALL TO ACCOMMODATE
ALL THE NEW MEMBERS.
[HENRIETTA]
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE,
BUT I THINK SHORYU MIGHT
HAVE DONE A LITTLE TOO MUCH
DURING THE RAID ON HAMELIN.
IT SEEMS LIKE ALL THE KIDS
WE PICKED UP ARE LIKE
BABY DUCKS WHO CONFUSE THEIR
FIRST TOY WITH THEIR MOTHER.
OH!
[SERARA] NYAN‐TA, WHAT
ARE YOU UP TO RIGHT NOW?
[MARIELLE] I STILL CAN'T
BELIEVE SHIROE TOTALLY
ORCHESTRATED THAT
RESCUE WHILE HE WAS
AT THE CONFERENCE.
I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS
DOING BOTH OF THOSE
THINGS AT ONCE EITHER.
HE REALLY DID RUN
THEM OUT OF THE
CITY LIKE HE SAID.
YOU KNOW THAT
SHIROE CAN BE, LIKE,
REALLY SCARY SOMETIMES.
HMM? YOU KNOW WHAT
JUST DAWNED ON ME?
WHERE'S EVERYONE
FROM LOG HORIZON?
[HENRIETTA] OH, ACTUALLY,
THEY'RE MOVING TODAY, TOO.
[MARIELLE] FOR REAL?
[NAOTSUGU]
HEY, SHIROE.
WHERE DO YOU WANT
THIS STUFF, MAN?
[SHIROE]
UH, OVER THERE, PLEASE.
HMM?
(HUMMING)
HEY. IT'S STARTING
TO SHAPE UP IN HERE.
[SHIROE]
KARASHIN?
HMM.
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT WAS HE HERE FOR?
[SHIROE] HE SUGGESTED HIRING
PEOPLE OF THE LAND AS
COURT REPORTERS FOR
THE ROUND TABLE.
HE'S GOT A POINT.
THEY'RE A LOT CHEAPER
THAN ADVENTURERS WOULD BE.
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN
HEARING A WILD RUMOR.
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
ARE ACTUALLY COMING TO
AKIHABARA BECAUSE
OF THE COOKING.
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THAT, DUDE?
MY LORD, A LOT OF THEM ARE
ALREADY INSIDE THE CITY,
AND I THINK IT'S SOMETHING
MORE THAN JUST IMMIGRATION.
HMM. I'D AGREE
WITH THAT.
[MISA] HE'S WRONG THIS TIME.
[KRUSTY] HUH?
[MISA]
SHIROE FROM LOG HORIZON
BELIEVES THE ROUND TABLE IS
GOING TO MAKE A DECISION
ABOUT GOING TO WAR AGAINST
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND, BUT
HE'S FORGETTING ONE THING.
THE SIDE WITH NUMERICAL
SUPERIORITY DECIDES.
[KRUSTY] AT LEAST THAT'S THE
WAY IT WORKS OUT HISTORICALLY.
WELL, VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES,
IT'S YOUR MOVE.
[SHIROE] WE SHOULD ASSUME
THEY'VE ALREADY STARTED.
HUH?
[MARIELLE] OH, MY GOODNESS!
[HENRIETTA] THIS IS AMAZING!
[MARIELLE] THIS PLACE IS HUGE!
[BOTH] HUH?
HA HA!
[HENRIETTA] OH, MY GOSH!
THIS NEW HAIRSTYLE
IS ADORABLE ON YOU.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE
OF CLEANING!
DON'T YOU WANT
TO SEE IT?
YOUR HOUSEWARMING GIFT? HA!
[HENRIETTA]
YOU'RE... GONNA...
[AKATSUKI] QUIT IT.
[SHIROE]
ARE YOU OK?
[NAOTSUGU]
IS SHE GONNA PUKE?
[MARIELLE] SHIROE, NAOTSUGU,
HOUSEWARMING GIFT!
TAKOYAKI, OKONOMIYAKI,
AND CREPES!
DID YOU HAVE TO DEEP
FRY THE DESSERT?!
YEAH, THERE'S TOO MUCH!
COME ON, SHIROE. YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO EAT A LOT,
OR YOU WON'T GROW
UP TO BE BIG AND
STRONG LIKE NAOTSUGU.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
BIG BOY?
HANG ON. DID YOU GO AND GET
BIGGER ON ME SOMEHOW, NAOTSUGU?
[NAOTSUGU] UH, NOT REALLY.
THAT'S, UH...
THAT'S NOT ME.
[AKATSUKI] LEAVE ME ALONE!
[SOJIRO] WELL, HEY.
THE GANG'S ALL HERE.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
WHOA! HEY, BABY!
HEY, THERE,
YOU GUYS!
WHAT'S UP?
LITTLE MAN, NAZNA,
WELCOME HOME, HUH?
WHAT'S SHAKING, BACON?
[AKATSUKI]
DO YOU KNOW THESE
TWO, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] MM‐HMM. NAZNA
WAS ALSO IN THE TEA
PARTY ALONG WITH SOJI.
[NAZNA]
THIS IS FOR YOU.
[NYAN‐TA] HMM?
[NAZNA] IT'S CHERRY SAKE
FROM OUR BREW MASTER.
WELL, NOW I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO THIS LIBATION.
[SOJIRO] YOUR GUILD HALL
IS AMAZING, GUYS.
[MARIELLE] TOTALLY TOTES.
IT MUST HAVE COST A FORTUNE.
[SHIROE]
NOT MUCH REALLY.
TAKE A LOOK.
THAT TREE DESTROYED THE
ELEVATOR HALLWAY AND STAIRS,
SO IT WAS EMPTY, AND WE GOT IT
CHEAPER THAN YOU'D EXPECT.
AND IT'S NOWHERE NEAR
THE CENTER OF THE CITY.
[HENRIETTA] HOW DID YOU
MANAGE TO GET THE ISSUES
WITH THE STAIRS
AND FLOORING FIXED?
[SHIROE] YEAH. I ASKED
MICHITAKA ABOUT THAT.
[MICHITAKA] I LIKE IT.
RENOVATING ALL THESE
RUN‐DOWN BUILDINGS
AND MAKING THEM USEFUL
AGAIN IS SOMETHING I CAN
TOTALLY GET BEHIND.
I DON'T LIKE
WASTED SPACE.
[SHIROE] SO WHAT DO
YOU THINK IT'LL COST?
HMM.
[NAOTSUGU]
AND, UH, REMEMBER,
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS HERE,
SO DON'T RIP US OFF.
I WOULDN'T KNOW HOW.
OTHER THAN A CRESCENT BURGER,
I DON'T REALLY KNOW
WHAT ANYTHING COSTS.
HUH?
IT'S NOT LIKE BUILDING AN
OFFICE OR A TRACK HOUSE.
ALL THIS STONE
AND MASON WORK IS
NEW TERRITORY FOR ME.
[HENRIETTA] SO WE REALLY
DON'T KNOW WHAT THE TRUE
VALUE OF OUR GOODS AND
SERVICES ARE, RIGHT NOW.
WHEN IT COMES
RIGHT DOWN TO IT,
THAT'S A PRETTY GLARING
HOLE IN ANY ECONOMIC SYSTEM.
[NAOTSUGU] OH, I
FORGOT TO TELL YOU.
ISAAC CAME BY.
YOU GOT A BIG
ENOUGH PLACE, GUYS.
[SHIROE] ISAAC!
HEY. VILLAIN IN GLASSES,
THIS IS JUST ENOUGH SPACE
TO LET MY SUMMONERS
GET SOME WORK IN HERE.
[SHIROE] HEY. WAIT
A SECOND, ISAAC.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[ISAAC] DO IT!
[SUMMONERS] HM!
(GIGGLING)
COSPLAY CHICKS!
AAH!
HUH?
HEH. LATER.
THE CLEANING SERVICE
IS FREE THIS TIME.
[SOJIRO]
UH, NOT VERY SOCIAL.
[NYAN‐TA] THEY'RE NOT
AS BAD AS ONE MIGHT LEAD
YOU TO BELIEVE, MK?
HMM.
[SOJIRO] WE'RE MAKING A HUGE
BATH OVER AT OUR PLACE.
WHY DON'T YOU DROP
IN WHEN IT'S DONE?
[SHIROE] SOUNDS GOOD.
[HENRIETTA] SEE YOU
SOON, AKATSUKI,
WHEN WE CAN TAKE
OUR TIME.
WELL, SHIROE, YOU'VE
BUILT A LOVELY HOUSE.
[NAZNA]
LATER! SEE YOU AROUND!
[MARIELLE]
LET'S GO.
[SHIROE] OH!
ARE TOYA AND MINORI
DOING OK WITH YOU GUYS?
[MARIELLE]
OH, WOW. THEY HAVEN'T
TOLD YOU ABOUT IT YET?
[SHIROE AND NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[MARIELLE] OH.
[HENRIETTA] HMM.
OH, IT'S NOTHING.
SEE YOU AT THE
NEXT MEETING!
MK...
[AKATSUKI] ARE YOU
GOING SHOPPING, MASTER?
I'M JUST PICKING UP A
FEW THINGS FOR DINNER.
IT'S EVERYONE'S
FAVORITE, CURRY TIME.
OHH! MY LORD,
DROP EVERYTHING!
WE'RE GONNA HAVE CURRY!
[SHIROE]
WHAT? CURRY?!
(AIRPLANE FLYBY)
(TIRES SQUEAL)
I LOVE CURRY, CHIEF!
HEY, NAOTSUGU!
IT'S CURRY TONIGHT!
[NAOTSUGU]
SERIOUSLY?! HA HA HA!
YEAH!
[NYAN‐TA] HEH. DON'T
YOU GO NOWHERE.
[ALL] HURRY BACK!
CURRY. OH, MY GOSH. CURRY.
[NAOTSUGU] MMM. I'M TRYING
TO DECIDE WHICH ONE I'D
RATHER HAVE STUFFED IN
MY MOUTH RIGHT NOW,
CURRY OR‐ OHH!
[NAOTSUGU] GOD!
MY LORD, MAY I PHYSICALLY
HUMILIATE THIS SCUMBAG?
WOULD YOU ONE TIME
LET ME FINISH?!
DO NOT BRING SHAME TO
THE GLORY OF CURRY!
[NAOTSUGU] THE CHIEF'S
CURRY IS FOR GROWNUPS.
IT'S FREAKING
SUPER‐MEGASPICY.
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT,
LITTLE BRITCHES?!
[AKATSUKI]
SHUT YOUR MOUTH HOLE.
[NAOTSUGU]
YOU'RE A MOUTH HOLE!
[BOTH] HEH.
(SIGHS)
I AM STARTING
A NEW GUILD.
WILL YOU JOIN ME?
[NAOTSUGU] UH... ZERO
SURPRISE FACTOR, DUDE.
WORST KEPT SECRET EVER.
FACE IT. WE'VE BEEN LIKE
A GUILD WITHOUT A NAME
SINCE WE GOT HERE.
I GUESS IT'S COOL YOU
REGISTERED AND EVERYTHING.
IT IS A NINJA'S
TASK TO SIMPLY
FOLLOW HER MASTER.
GIVE ME YOUR ORDERS,
AND I WILL FOLLOW
THEM TO THE END.
HMM.
[AKATSUKI] I WILL...
I WILL HAVE CURRY, AND...
AND THERE'S NOTHING
YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT!
[MAN 1] LOOKING
FOR PARTY MEMBERS!
[MAN 2] WE'RE LEAVING
TOMORROW MORNING!
[MAN 1] MAN, IF WE COULD JUST
RECRUIT ONE MORE GOOD GUY.
[PLAYER] YOU GUYS SHOULD
JUST JOIN MY PARTY INSTEAD.
[OTHERS] HUH?
I'M STILL WORKING OUT
ALL THE DETAILS,
BUT THIS IS PERFECT.
IT WAS DESTINY
FOR US TO MEET.
REALLY NICE TIMING, GUYS.
[OTHERS] HUH?
[MAN 1] UH, WHAT
LEVEL ARE YOU ANYWAY?
HA! LEVEL 20.
[MAN 2]
UH, YEAH. DON'T CALL US.
WE'LL CALL YOU,
LIKE, UH, NEVER.
WHAT?! COME ON!
[NAOTSUGU] THERE WILL BE
NO MILD CURRY, PEEWEE!
SPICY IS
FOR WEAKLINGS.
[NYAN‐TA]
GUESS WHO'S BACK.
[GROUP] HUH?
[AKATSUKI] YOU'RE
BACK ALREADY, MASTER?
[NAOTSUGU] UH, W‐WE'RE STILL
GONNA HAVE CURRY TONIGHT,
AREN'T WE, CHIEF?
THESE TWO APPEARED TO BE
ADMIRING OUR HANDIWORK
ON THE HOUSE,
SO I THOUGHT
I'D LET THEM HAVE
A CLOSER LOOK.
TOYA, MINORI.
[SHIROE] I HEARD THAT
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
WAS MOVING TODAY.
[MINORI]
WE, UM...
[TOYA]
WELL, IT'S
LIKE THIS.
WE CAME HERE... UH...
WE'RE HERE BECAUSE ME AND
MY SISTER WANT TO BECOME
MEMBERS OF YOUR GUILD!
OH!
WE'D LIKE YOU TO
TEACH US INSTEAD OF
THE CRESCENT MOON
ALLIANCE, SHIROE.
MISS MARIELLE AND EVERYONE
WITH HER GUILD WERE REALLY
NICE TO US AND ALL,
BUT WE WANT TO GO ON
ADVENTURES WITH YOU.
OH.
[TOYA] WE MADE IT THROUGH
ALL THE STUFF WE WENT
THROUGH BECAUSE
YOU TAUGHT US HOW.
WE WANT TO BE IN
THE GUILD YOU CREATED,
BROTHER SHIROE!
I KNOW I'M WEAK NOW,
BUT I WANT TO GET
STRONGER WITH YOUR HELP!
WE KNOW WE'RE NOT
AS STRONG AS THE
REST OF YOU ARE,
BUT WE REALLY
WANT TO LEARN!
PLEASE TEACH US,
SO WE CAN BE AN ASSET
AND NOT SLOW YOU DOWN.
[MINORI]
LET US JOIN YOU!
WHA‐? I, UH... HMM.
[NYAN‐TA] SHIROECHI...
[SHIROE] AH.
[NYAN‐TA] COME ON.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE
STARING AT THEM, FOOL.
YOU'RE THE GUILD MASTER.
AH...
[SHIROE, THINKING]
A GUILD MASTER...
I GUESS THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENED WHEN I REGISTERED.
OK. GUESS I AM.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
RIGHT. IT'S MY TURN
TO LEAD EVERYONE.
ALL RIGHT. I AM LOOKING
FOR A FIGHTER AND A CLERIC.
WELCOME TO LOG HORIZON!
[TOYA] YAH!
[MINORI] OHH!
AND FOR YOUR VERY
FIRST ASSIGNMENT,
I'M GONNA NEED YOU
GUYS TO EAT CURRY WITH
THE SENIOR MEMBERS.
GOT IT?
[TOYA] YES, SIR!
[MINORI] NO PROBLEM!
[NYAN‐TA] MMM. LET'S
MAKE THE CURRY FIRST.
HEH HEH.
[NAOTSUGU]
OH, YEAH!
[AKATSUKI] NOTHING BEATS A PLATE
OF CURRY UNDER A NIGHT SKY.
[NYAN‐TA] AHH. JUST WISH
I HAD SOMETHING TO GO WITH IT.
NEXT TIME, I'LL MAKE
SOME CURRY RELISH, BABY.
[NAOTSUGU] I WANT TO
HAVE YOUR BABY, CHIEF!
(BOTH LAUGH)
HUH?
[MAN]
A ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE?
I SEE.
THE ADVENTURERS
ARE ORGANIZING.
[MAID]
LORD SERJIAD.
HMM?
I'VE BROUGHT YOU
LADY RAYNESHIA AS YOU
ORDERED, YOUR GRACE.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
PEACE HAS COME TO AKIHABARA.
MINORI AND TOYA
JOIN LOG HORIZON
AND TRAIN EVERY DAY.
SHIROE DECIDES
TO HOLD A TRAINING
CAMP FOR NEW PLAYERS.
MEANWHILE, A LETTER
COMES TO THE ROUND TABLE.
IT'S FROM THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND.
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.