Your mission--should
you choose to accept it--
is to distract your
boss for five seconds,
so he doesn't notice the
pandemonium going on upstairs.
I'll lay on the woman-charm!
And if that doesn't work...
I'll bust out the guns!
Those'll do.
Double-O Eight is on it!
You're starting with charm...?
Can't you tell?
Fire at will.
Target in sight...!
Bullseye!
We're clear!
Begin the experiment!
What the hell...?! Bastard!
It didn't work... My bad...
Are they runnin' a
damn circus up there?!
Why'd it stop?
They must've
heard him... Unless...
Are you... telling me...?!
I'm telling ya.
Huh?
For the last time!
Wait... so let me
get this straight...
the 42-inch TV down there
has been acting as the
lifter all this time...?
And only D-mails sent
out while it was on
during business hours
actually made it back...?
Y'know, that explains a lot!
Try to connect the dots
more quietly, would you?...
Your poor head.
'Twas brains against Braun...
I can't believe he
actually hit me...
I'm kind of surprised
it took him this long.
You're the one who wanted to run
the experiment, lest we forget--
At any rate... you found
a big piece in the Phone
Wave functionality puzzle...
Yeah... that does explain a lot.
In other words,
it's time we try to send someone
into the past physically.
Nope.
You know you could at
least pretend to consider it!
You can't compress a human
being down to 36 bytes...
You do remember SERN's subjects
turning to pudding don't y--
Nobody likes a braggart.
Bragging to you? That's rich...
Look at the title.
"An Analysis of Neural
Pulse Signals in Relation
to Memories Stored
in the Temporal Lobe."
If that's just the
title, I'm scared!
Basically... it's all about
the wiring of our memories...
The science of the brain
is kinda... my thing.
Oh...
Long story short,
the brain stores our memories in
the form of electrical impulses.
It's just data, like any other.
"Just data..."
Are you saying--?!
I am... Physically
sending a human being
back in time is out
of the question...
But maybe we
can find a way
to send their memories
back, as a work-around.
Into their phone?
No. That's the thing
we need to figure out...
We'd have to convert
their memories
into data and send
it like a D-mail...
but instead of a phone, it goes
into their past self's head.
Then you become
your earlier you...!
It's more like consciousness-
hopping than time-travel.
It's me.
This is the culmination
of our research...
The master plan is poised
for its great unveiling!
Named for a Norn of yore...
begin Operation Verdandi!
Say what?
Terrific. What harebrained
scheme do you have for us now?
We're going to
field-test the process
you just delineated to
us--try to stay on task!
It's not as
easy as that--
I'm gonna need to find all sorts
of supplemental equipment...
That said... we
are in Akihabara,
so it shouldn't be too big
of a hassle to locate
most of the instruments.
And if we're only reading
the temporal lobe... I mean...
What's the problem?
Well, it's just that the
Phone Wave probably can't
compress all that data without
a bunch of add-ons. That's all.
And...
And what?
Nothing. All right... Here
are all the parts I'll need.
So... what is it that
we're gonna try and do...?
Let me see if I can simplify
Christina's version for you.
We can... graft
your current mind
onto the mind of
your former self.
Hmmm...
Sounds kinda scary to me...
Maybe, we should just stick
with the D-mail instead...
Well unfortunately...
with D-mail there are too
many variables at play...
One message can lead to any
number of unforeseen changes...
But how is sending
memories back any better?
Knowing the future
they came from,
hopefully a person wouldn't
choose to alter too much.
Take the current transformed
state of Akihabara.
It's a perfect example of this.
Of what?
Nothing. Never mind.
Um... what happens to this you
after your memories
get sent back?
'Cause your
body's still here...
Is your head all empty or what?
Hmm... that's a good question...
And also... y'know
how we're having
this conversation
right now, Okarin...?
Yeah.
Okay, so... pretend that
my brain goes back in time
a whole week, and
I do the week over...
What happens if we don't have
this conversation the
second time around...?
In that case... I assume...
you'd remember this talk
but not I...
Because for me, the whole thing
never would have taken place.
So... I'd remember it
just fine, but for you...
it wouldn't exist at all...
That's how it works?
I think so.
If that happened...
I think that I would cry.
For me?
Nuh-uh. For me, silly.
Ooh, look...! It's Moeka!
Hey, Moeka!
Shining Finger. You look
even more serious than usual.
"Did you drop the
time-travel thing?"
Nope, we're still doing it...!
An' guess what!
Now we can do a time-leap
with someone's memories!
Don't just blurt it out!
Awww! But Moeka's a lab
member--she's Double-O Five!
Yeah, but still... Huh?
What do you think it is?
As the name clearly implies...
one's memories go
leaping back in time!
Memories...?
Uh, Moeka...?
Wait... where ya going...?
I hope she's okay...
I guess checking Akibaoo
first would make sense...
Heya, Mayuri!
I'm glad to see you too,
Nae...! Where'd you come from?
How's it hanging?
You've been walking
around like that?!
Yeah, I know...
The boss said
my punishment was to wear
it for the rest of the day.
You look like someone
off of Street Fighter.
As if!
This get up is way too
flimsy for hand-to-hand combat.
Huh?
Oh! I'm just saying, is all...
Anyway, we're out here 'cause
Nae has something to tell you.
S'that so?
M-hmmm...
I'm sorry... My dad
shouldn'ta been so mean before.
It's okay...
You tracked me down
to tell me that...?
Aren't you a
considerate little creature.
Aw, don't be rude, Okarin...
Thank you, Nae...
But I've been a thorn
in your father's side
since the day I moved in...
Kinda had it coming.
Not like you to be
so patient with her.
What do you mean?
He's a very patient person...!
Suuuure.
Well anyway, I'll see both of
you back at the lab later on.
Are you off to meet somebody?
Uh-huh! My cosplay
friend Fubuki!
I made her an outfit!
Oh yeah--Comima
is almost upon us.
Yup! I can't wait...!
Have a good afternoon!
Too-too-roo!
See ya...!
Well, you wanna head
back up to the lab?
No... Probably better not...
Christina sent me out
to scavenge for parts.
I wasn't going to tell you
this... but she works for SERN.
Christina, a SERN
mole? Doubtful...
Knight Heart's been busy lately.
Totally.
Huh?!!
How long have you
been standing there?!
Long enough to take in
your dirty little secret.
Oh now, now...!
I was just...
My dear, you've
nothing to be ashamed of!
It's not like...?!
Embrace your true
nature, assistant!
Uh... Whatever.
Excellent... I dub thee...
Christina, reigning
queen of fan forums.
I don't need any more
nicknames from you...!
Just don't tell
the others, please?!
Oh, come on...
Why keep that juicy
tidbit to yourself,
when you should be
putting it on your CV...!
Right under your publications,
tack on your best posts!
You are such a jerk.
Guilty...! So what was
tonight's rousing adventure?
Double checking your AMA thread?
I hate that I know
what that means!
Actually this bodes
rather well for you.
I know it comes as
a relief to me...
Anyone who can't cover
their internet tracks
can't possibly be a spy.
Ha-ha... Real funny.
Well, Suzuha
intimated that you were
a SERN operative when
I ran into her earlier.
You know damn well
that I'm no such thing.
That girl's being ridiculous.
Of course she is.
Anyone could see you're really
a spy from the Organization...
You had a change of heart
and joined forces with the very
lab you were sent to neutralize.
Also wrong.
Anyway, how is the
evolution coming along?
Evolution?
Of the Phone Wave!
You know, all those
parts you had me buy?!
Oh yeah... That... I'll get
on it. Too late to say no...
Why so hesitant now...?
Getting cold feet are we?
Who wouldn't...?
I'm worried about what'll
happen if we actually do this.
But it's...
more than just that.
Go on.
As much as I don't want
to have this conversation,
I guess it's kind of unfair
to keep you in the dark.
Not here, though... I can't
look at you when I say it.
Okay, so... things between my
dad and I... are kinda rough...
Stuck by lightning on the
wind-swept veldt of Arkansas,
your once-doting father
succumbe--
Y'know what?! Just forget it!
Tell me more... I'll be good.
Basically...
my dad dislikes me.
No... he hates me.
Not as his child, but as
a scientist... As a rival.
He's a physicist... Well, was...
When I was little,
I loved to hear him talk about
the intricacies of his work.
By the time I was
in middle school,
I understood the
science behind the talk.
That's when I started
writing scientific papers
and winning a bunch
of awards of my own.
But I didn't care
about the awards...
I liked that it was our thing.
We'd share papers over
e-mail, debating ideas.
But then... the e-mails
stopped... Suddenly, nothing.
I had been knocking down his
theories... one after the next.
Pointing out his mistakes...
I'd shamed him...
Emasculated him...
He got mean.
To Mom. To his peers.
Academia kicked
him to the curb.
The last time I saw him, what
he said, word for word, was:
"I don't need your pity.
How dare you look down on me?"
"I'm your dad,
you little... bitch."
I don't think he can hate me
any more than he already does...
but if I create a
time-leap device...
I'm sure he'll find a way.
And that's why you've
been dragging your feet.
Don't worry, though. I said I'm
going to build it, and I will.
Because I love to experiment...
I can't not put a good
hypothesis to the grindstone.
Always testing things...
Like father, like daughter,
I guess... I'm glad.
In that case,
let us begin Operation
Verdandi without delay...!
We haven't any
time to waste...!
The Organization snaps
at our very heels!
That's your reply...?
What other reply should one
expect of Hououin Kyouma?!
I shall not rest until
the world rests in my palm!
Why'd I even bother?
Which is why I'm
going to fix this!
Where is your father now?
Huh...? Oh... in Aomori, why?
Travel will be expensive,
but no matter.
Merely pick the day, and
I will free up my schedule.
Whoa, wait...!
We're gonna go see my dad...?!
Of course we are...!
You are undoubtedly
a top-notch scientist,
but my ambitions require you
to be unfettered by regret!
To that end, I, Hououin
Kyouma, will accompany you
and broach the subject
with sublime subtlety
so as to clear the noxious
air 'twixt father and child.
Wait a sec...
So you're telling me, just when
I get used to you being an ass,
you're gonna
say something nice?
Well, only insofar... as...
What's so funny?!
Y'know what the
trouble is with you?
Sometimes you're a good guy.
If you're done singing
my praises, can we work?
Yeah, yeah...
And no wussing out--you're
in this with me even
if I have to drag you
kicking and screaming.
I doubt you'll have to.
Too... too... roo...
Are you okay, Mayuri?
Those bags look really heavy...
Where's that Okarin guy
should've tagged along
and made himself useful.
Nah, I'm fine...
Just a little bit farther...!
Don't gimme that crap...!
I wrote "Makise,"
on here plain as day!
I assumed it meant
"Makise Pudding"!
You know, like a brand name
or perhaps some secret code
as to its pro-biotic
properties...
You are so full of it!
Who is this Makise chap, anyway?
It's me, dammit!
Well, see, there's the rub...
If you'd only deigned to
write "Christina" on the lid,
we could have avoided
this whole pudding fracas...
You've one too many aliases.
I shouldn't have to write
anything, ya big mooch!
Eat your own food...!
Wait, is that my spoon?!
I don't recall you
signing anything
in triplicate before
using the lab's forks!
Hey, it's me...
Hey. Whatcha got there?
A bunch of cosplay materials
and all my sleepover stuff!
You're crashing here?
Yup...! So... I figured I'd
bring some cosplay work along!
Is this okay with your
parents...? Did you ask first?
I just told 'em you'd be
here, too, so it's fine!
You're staying over to
upgrade the Phone Wave, right?
Oh... Well,
that was the plan,
but I might have to
take a rain check...
It seems that we've got a
pudding thief running around...
"Hououin something or other"--
I really can't be bothered
to remember it exactly.
It's Kyouma...!
Hououin Kyouma! Pay attention!
Oh, like you're such a
superstar with names!
At least mine is real!
Maybe I shouldn't
spend the night...
No. I don't mind
sticking around.
So long as pudding thief here
is sleeping somewhere else.
What did you say?!
My soul is tied to
these very floorboards...!
We are as one!
Why do I have to do the shopping
for their stupid sleepover...?
Some trick of fate has left me
as my own
assistant's errand boy...
What? Speak of the devil...
Hmph! "Don't get too cocky...
After all, you are talking
to a mad scientist."
Yeah, says the
reigning king of cocky.
Huh...? What, now?
Oh, nothing!
Don't worry about it!
C'mon--we gotta do this
before Okabe gets back!
Right!
More demands, I assume?
Oh my god...!
Mayuri...!
Mayuri...! Mayuri...!
You...!
I can't believe you!
You are such an asshole!
Shame on you...
I could see Daru doing something
like that, maybe, but not you.
Look at you...!
In such a hurry to ogle us,
you didn't even
remember to get snacks...!
What is your
problem, anyway...?!
You okay?
Okarin...?
Hey... Daru!
I thought you'd gone
home for the day.
Yeah. I called it.
I tried to log in from
my home computer...
but uh, the lab
PC wouldn't allow it.
What's the issue?
Well, it's spoken for,
'cause we're already
connected... To SERN.
What...?! So we've been
connected all this time?
Maybe. I dunno...
I'd like to chalk it up
to my badass hacking,
but I really have no
idea what's up with this.
It's like they left the
door wide open for us,
or something...
They did what?
Hold on a sec...!
If you aren't the one
who plugged us into SERN,
then... who's to say it's not
them hacking into our system.
Maybe they wanna see what
we've been up to all this time.
It's possible, but I covered
my tracks like a boss...
On the upside, we
can use the LHC--
Could it be... them...?!
We can do that?
Whatcha looking at?
There a problem
with your phone?
No... no, it's nothing...