Yesterday... after I'd come
back from Mr. Braun's house...
Nothing... Not so much
as car backfiring.
Up to that point...
The thirteenth had
always been D-day.
I think telling myself
not to follow Suzuha
got us close enough
to the one percent...
Maybe... Hopefully...
Just please...
Please let this
be the one where...
Oh no!
I just wound you a while ago.
Don't tell me your broken...
So not fair.
I've taken extra special
care of you and everything.
Okay. You've got my attention...
Why are you brooding?
Help me...
She's going to die
- in two hours?!
Wait... Hold on a second...
You've been time-leaping like a
madman to trying to stop it...
haven't you?
Must've been horrible.
Alright, help me think...
What have we got...?
We know that Suzuha
feels we can spare Mayuri
by shifting the alpha
attractor field we're currently
in to a beta world-line.
'Course, to do that...
We'd need to hack
into SERN's database
and delete every shred of intel
they have on the laboratory,
which means we'd need the IBN.
That's the thing...
It'd been in storage at
the Yanabayashi Shrine
before Moeka's D-mail...
Now though?
Needle in a haystack.
Just bear with me for a sec:
A whopping total of five
D-mails started all of this...
The lottery one;
Kiryuu's; Ruka's; Faris'...
The one about Suzuha...
Apparently undoing that last one
gave you a little wiggle room...
It postponed the lab
raid by twenty hours...
Pretty significant, yeah?
I mean, it's enough
to have me wonder
whether or not undoing all
the texts in reverse order...
might pop us back
to a world-line where
the IBN's accounted for...
I'm just shooting in the dark...
But hey, for a
working hypothesis
we could do a lot worse.
Yes we could.
If there's even the
ghost of chance...
I feel like I shouldn't
let you do this...
You're a gauge-twitch
from meltdown as it is...
I've no illusions about the
risk to my mental health...
But I have to do
what I have to do.
Just be careful.
Don't read into that!
Your brain simply represents
a specimen totally
invaluable to our...
to mankind's understanding of
time travel's neurological...
Thank you, Kurisu.
You just called
me by my name...
That's certainly
a first... So...
You're suddenly nice when
I'm about to forget everything.
What?
Nothing.
Back to front. What's the next
one that needs to be undone?
The one we allowed
Faris to send.
Wassabi?
Look, don't freak out:
I need to know where you
think Faris would be right now.
I know where she is right now.
Yeah...? Go on, then!
Well, the last match of the
Rai-Net ABGC just wrapped,
so smart money says
she's at the UPX Building.
ABGC?
Ugh! You're killin'
me, old man...
Stands for Access Battler's
Grand Championship?
Collective Rai-Netter
throw-down
for every qualifier
in the country?
Which Our Lady of the
Immaculate Cat Ears just won,
I should add.
Just focus on the
task at hand...
And remember:... You don't
know what her text said...
Only that it
transformed Akihabara
from a Moe cultural Mecca
to... well, to this.
Kyouma!
What in the hell?! Faris!
'Fraid she's latched on
some douche bag in lab coat.
Cat's outta the bag, huh...?
Oh well. Bitch can run,
but she can't hide.
'Cause nobody--nobody...
wrangles free of the Cid.
Who are these chodes?
They call themselves
Viral Attackers.
Okay, then...
Look the least you
need to know is that
they're a gang of
hardcore Rai-Netters
who'd sooner drown a puppy
than lose a tournament to me.
They've been waiting in ambush
since they got booted
out of the championship.
Surely they can be
reasoned with...?
Over here!
The hell'd they go?
They're not ninjas.
They're here somewhere.
Gotcha.
C'mon.
Oh yeah... since we're here:
what'd you call me for earlier?
Oh, yes...! I need to know
what your D-mail said.
My what?
The text we let you
send back in time.
Oh, baby doll...
Did you fall on your head?
Wait, of course.
The Faris of this world-line
hasn't the first clue
what D-mail is.
I... That is to say...
Got 'em!
Okay, speaking
hypothetically,
if I'd told you we'd
invented a time machine,
would you believe me?
Duh, you know your
word is law with me!
Really?!
I just put the
finishing touches on a
kickass inter-dimensional
transporter myself...
Right, starting over. Imagine
Akihabara as a MOE hotspot.
Huh?
Let's... just... suppose
you used a time machine
to create the silicon
gulch it's become.
How would you have
accomplished that?
Is this like prisoner's
base or something?
Don't over-think it,
just tell me!
Um... I have no idea
what I could've done...
If this town was
brimming with moe,
I probably wouldn't
have changed it.
You'll laugh...
But back in the day I wanted
to open a maid cafe...
I begged daddy till
I was blue in the face...
even told him I'd finance it...
Ah, but you know the drill:
no little girl of his, right?
Yes, Queen May's...
How'd you know what
I wanted to call it?
I never even told dad!
Because it really existed!
Right here in downtown...!
This city used to be the
Canterbury for otakus!
It had all that stuff!
It what??
Believe me when I say
no one loved this place
more than you...!
But every corner of
it changed the moment
we let you send that
text into the past!
What on Earth did it say?!
Please...! It's a
matter of life...!
Guys! This way!
What are you looking at?
Take it in... Queen May's was
located on this very spot...
This is where your
dream became a reality.
What?
You didn't just run the place.
You lived it; breathed it.
Mayuri, too!
Wild horses couldn't
keep Daru away.
Matter of fact...
This is where we first met.
Welcome home, Meow-ster!
Iced coffee, please.
Coming up in two
shakes of a kitten's tail!
The competition for the
Faris Cup is about to begin...
Special codename...
Bitchin'!
K. B. O. O. M!
Otherwise known
as KAH-BOOM!
Faris!
I'm okay.
Tell me what's at stake
if you can't undo the text.
Someone's life. ...Mayuri's.
You're kidding me...
You're just making all this up!
Mayushii couldn't be killed
over some stupid random text!
Damn it, what was in
the message you sent?!
I have to know! If I don't
undo it, she's dead!
I can't tell you.
The hell do you mean...?!
Faris, please...!
She's your friend!
Don't you care if she dies?!
Of course I care...!
It's just...
It's just what?!
I don't want to lose
my daddy again...
He died ten years ago...
The message you let
me send saved his life.
Kyouma!
Oh god, no...
Not the badass you
thought you were, huh dude?
Sorry, princess.
This jackass can't help you.
Let go of me! Kyouma...! No!
Cat's in the cradle, boss.
Excellent!!!
Again the tingling 'round...
Hear that? He's excited...
What do you say we celebrate?
Stop this...
...will soon be eating pureed
humble pie through a straw!
Lookie here.
Let her go.
Kyouma!
Oh, I see...
We're still on, huh?
Well, I'm game if you are.
No...! Stop it...!
Please! Stop!!!
Oh shit!
Abort! Abort! Abort!
Daddy!
Hold it, punks!
What were you up to here?!
Wait. Where'd you guys go?
The hell...
Shit. That the cops?
Ah... well... Son of a bitch.
Thank heavens...
Seems I made it just in time.
Daddy... Thank you...
I rushed to the center when I
heard you'd won the tournament,
but you'd already taken off.
And then you weren't
answering your phone...
Next time, young lady,
I expect you to be a little
easier for me to get a hold of.
And you, son...
Well frankly, I'm having trouble
finding the words to thank you.
Please, sir; I was
less than useless.
You're too modest, Okabe,
but I'm afraid the fact is,
my not being there put
both of you in harm's way...
Oh stop...
Don't talk like that.
You had work;
you couldn't help it.
It's okay, Rumiho...
An old 5100, you say?
Yes... I heard you gave
one away some time ago...
Any idea where it is...?
I mean, could you
by chance get it back?
Life had other ideas...
I never meant to break
my promise to Hashida...
Hashida...? But surely
you don't mean Suzuha!
You knew her...?
I came by the 5100 to begin
with because of that woman.
That IBN 5100 is as good
as mine--you'll see...!
I'll make sure it gets
to you guys in one piece.
How 'bout that... She did it...
She really came through...
It's okay... You can tell
him the whole story.
You sure, sweetheart...?
Daddy, he totally put his
life on the line for me.
Rumiho... was kidnapped
when she was a girl.
My little empire wasn't the
behemoth it is now, you see...
The ransom demanded
far exceeded my means...
Then out of the blue...
Someone offered to take the IBN
off my hands at an
exorbitant sum
and I wasn't about to look
a gift horse in the mouth.
Understandable...
So of course you sold it?
You bet I did. The money
gave me back my daughter.
Since then...
I've made it a personal rule
never to renege on a promise
I've made to my little girl...
Not for all the tea in China...
Never ever.
Oh, daddy...
I don't want to lose
my daddy again...
He died ten years ago...
The message you let
me send saved his life.
How can I ask her
to do such a thing...?
It's just inhuman.
Please don't send
another one, Okarin...!
If you press that button,
it's like none of
this was ever real!
If I... If I don't...
then Mayuri will...
May I come in?
Yeah, sure.
Faris, I...
Hey... Thanks for
stickin' up for me...
Those people were terrifying...
I'm not sure what they would've
done if you hadn't been there,
but I'm sure it would've
been unpleasant. You're a hero.
Oh, come now...
I'm sure their bark was
worse than their bite.
Don't blow me off,
I'm trying to be serious
for a minute here.
Sorry.
Listen, Faris... What I said...
I think it'd be better
if you call me Rumiho.
Kyouma... or... maybe
I should call you Okabe now...
You probably saved
my life out there.
Don't get all real on me...
Call me what you always do.
Look, whatever okay...?
Thank you for what you did...
You're my... knight
in shining armor.
Ah...! No pressure...!
Trust me... I'm no knight.
Lunatic perhaps;
but knight? I think not.
Level with me.
Does Mayushii's life
really hang in the balance?
Yeah.
When I was eight... I wanted
to celebrate my birthday...
I made daddy promise
to drop everything
and come home
to join the party...
But... He ended up canceling
for a business trip.
It wasn't his fault...
but I was so upset...
I thought he loved his job
more than me, you know...?
I was so mad, I told him
I wished he was dead...
And when he heard
how upset I was,
he caugh an early flight back.
And I never saw him again.
Your D-mail kept him from
getting on that plane...
And the city transformed
because he lived
to shoot down
your maid cafe idea...
You sacrificed it all just to
have your dad see you grow up.
It was pretty nice,
you know...? While it lasted.
Faris. Rumihio...
I'll undo it... Okay?
Dad died ten years ago
in a plane crash...
That's the reality...
Every father-daughter
moment we've shared since
has been on borrowed time...
Not that I wouldn't
move heaven and earth
to keep the lie going...
But there's always a price
for this kind of thing.
And I can't let Mayuri pay it.
Are you... Are you sure?
No I'm not sure...
How could I be?
I feel like I'm
going to be sick;
it's like two worlds are
all tangled up in my head...
It's crazy...!
I can remember all these details
from both sides of the change.
They all feel so real and so
unreal at the same time...
How do I do this...?
How do I do this?!
Damn it, look... I can't let you
go through with this, okay...?
I'll talk to Kurisu; she's
bound to know an alternative!
No! No one's jumping through any
more stupid hoops because me...!
It's not fair to any of us!
It's time... I have to
accept life as it is...
I... owe it to myself, right?
Just give me a minute to
be weak, though... Okay?
Of course.
So, did she...?
Yes. She was very brave.
Are we set?
Meow meow...! Oh, my...
Somebody's mister
sad-face right now.
What's wrong with you?
So, uh... When we jump back
to the prior world-line,
am I gonna lose my
memories of this one?
I don't know...
You said earlier you
had memories of things
from both sides of
the change, right...?
So you'll probably keep them.
That's a relief.
Don't take this weird...
But this whole
thing between us...?
I wanna keep hold of it.
I'm sure you will.
We're fired up... Go for it!
Good-bye... Daddy.
Kyouma!
Please tell me you've seen
my cell phone lying around.
Faris...
Mayushii has no idea,
so by process of elimination,
I figure you have to
know where it is, right?
You rascal...!
You've been poring
over my private texts...!
Have you no decency...?!
Does the fairer sex's privacy
account for so little to a man?
Come on, Kyouma!
Don't just stand there
and take it, fire back...!
Ask me what a lady might
have to hide... Ugh!
Oh, Faris...
Hey, hey! Hands off
the girl, Casanova!
You don't get to
manhandle every female
who wanders into your lab.
It's just camaraderie.
In another life we battled
darkness most sinister
to arise arm-in-arm
from the ashes
of a peril beyond
mortal reckoning!
You must be some warrior.
Oh, Faris honey.
You're as loony as he is. Wow.
I'm sorry...
Faris' ordeal was pointless...
The IBN is still missing.
She stored it at the shrine
ten years ago, as before.
And up until a year back it
was still there, but now...
Now there's no
telling where it is.