But to keep
Mayuri alive...
To return to that version of
fate... Makise Kurisu...
...must die...
Alright. Let's
delete this puppy.
Stop!
It isn't necessary.
It can't be.
Where's Okabe?
No idea. Been too busy to
keep tabs on him.
Break a leg out
there, Mayushii!
Same to you, soldier!
Peace out!
So I take this is the last
day of Comima?
Yup. You should totally
come with me...!
There's so much adorable
cosplay to scope out!
Uh... I'm... pretty sure
it'd wouldn't be my thing.
Where did Okarin run off to?
Your guess is as good
as mine, sweetie;
who knows what rock
he's under...
Or why he called
off the hack.
It's gonna get up to like
a million degrees today.
Even mad scientists
have to keep hydrated
if they don't want a visit
from Uncle Heat Stroke.
You going back to
Comima I assume?
Yup! Wouldn't miss it.
Yes, well. Be careful.
K.
There... That'll give you a
little shade... See you later!
Wait...!
Think it through, Okabe...
Every D-mail undone has
pushed Mayuri's death
back another
twenty-four hours...
Originally it occurred
on the thirteenth;
undoing Suzuha's text
moved it to the fourteenth...
Then Faris',
Ruka's, Moeka's...
Every reversal has
bought us a day...
Which means if I'm
doing the math right,
on this world-line Mayuri will
die at 8 o'clock on August 17th.
Today.
Okarin!
I'd say it sounds like you
honed in on your quarry.
Uh-huh! Good thing
I found 'em when I did:
they were almost sold
out! Daru's gonna flip!
Oh... They have this
cool art book on some
mecha show I'd never seen,
too... You should come see!
Oh... I Believe I'll pass.
Are you sure...?
I could take you to it.
Thank you, no...
I'm a bit preoccupied.
Poor Okarin...
Well, if there is anything you
wanna see, I know the layout.
Dully noted.
We can leave... I mean, if...
Bah...! Come now,
don't be absurd...
When I say "preoccupied,"
I'm referring to my never-ending
vigil against the Organization,
who, I've grok-ed from
various trustworthy sources,
have set this place crawling
with specially trained
ninja assassins.
Perfect place for
them, really...
They blend with the costumed
crowd like cephalopods.
Wow... Sounds like they go to
an awful lot of trouble, huh?
I'm going to try and
get the drop on them.
Reconvene here at
1500 hours, understood?
Sir!
Oh, hey...!
They've got a concession
stand just a little ways down
from the entrance!
Five hours... Stiff upper lip...
Push through to an answer...
You've got to keep
Mayuri from dying
without jumping from
this world-line.
You expect me to go near his
stuff without a hazmat suit...
Okay, okay. Slow down.
Just... Give me a second.
These bookshelves
look like a war zone.
Would it be a thick as a normal
directory, you think, or--?
I am totally gonna sue.
Yeah
It's me.
What have you guys found
out...? Any progress?
Progress? We're at
standstill day three.
You told us to hold off.
And now'd be a
good time to know why.
What exactly's going on?
Mayuri... dies today.
Yeah. We've
established that...
It's the whole reason we
wanna hack into SERN...
The first text that
jumped back in time--
No...! That's no longer our tac!
I'm puzzling out a
way to save Mayuri
that doesn't involve our having
to reverse anything else.
But why?
Because... there have been
unforeseen developments.
Okay. Such as?
Look, I can't explain
at the moment...
There's an alternative;
I'm going find it.
That's all you need to know.
Why are you talking like it's--
Stop grilling me--!
Stop leaving me in the dark!
Listen, I want to help you;
but I can't do that if you play
things so close to the chest.
It's happening soon, isn't it?
Damn it, Okabe
give me something!
Man, my feet are super sore.
Worth it, though.
Hey, mind if we pop by
the lab for some snacks?
I don't know about you,
but I could eat a house
right about now.
You okay...? You look tired.
Uh...
It's almost time...
Oh god...
What am I gonna do...?
I'd opt for the two of us
breaking into a run, but...
Okarin?
Let's go.
'Kay. Weird question...
Why'd you tag along
with me today?
You didn't really look very
much, and, well you know...
That is kinda the whole reason
for coming to these things
in the first place; plus you
had me to show you around...
It's not every day
I get to be the one
who knows more about
something than you do.
I don't know...
I'm still glad you
came, though.
This was the first time you and
I have been to Comima together.
I'm totally marking
it on my calendar.
Mayuri...
In point of fact...
I'd pinned my hopes on
seeing Rukako blushing
in some wildly
inappropriate cosplay.
Shame he was a no-show.
No kidding!
People would've been
swarming around him.
He'd've had his own fan club!
Without a doubt.
Every blog on the interwebs
would be flooded with pics.
Heh. And people would
see that adorable face.
And they'd say to
all their friends:
"make way for the
next big thing!"
And, and, once
he got all famous,
you and me and the gang could
say we knew him back when.
There's not a detail about that
scenario doesn't ring true.
You know, I think if you
ever did a cosplay
you'd be just as popular.
Perhaps one day.
Are you serious?
Mind you, I'd only
consider it on condition
that we cosplay as a team.
Okay!
But, of course...
Warming Christina to the idea
might prove a bit problematic...
Getting the others on board
would be cinch comparatively,
though; and she'd follow
their lead eventually...
That accomplished,
we shall descend upon
an unsuspecting
Comima in full regalia,
the infamous Hououin
Kyouma in all his glory
as the group's
dazzling Axis Mundi!
Yeah, well... We better
start planning our outfits...
Kurisu might be easier to
convince than you think.
Tell you what: I'll work on her,
you focus on everybody else.
An excellent--
Oh no...! I just wound you.
Don't tell me you're broken...
So not fair... I've
taken extra special--
Okarin?!
Damn it, no! I'm not
going to watch this again!
What do you
want from me?!
Okarin?!
Just stay here!
I don't...
This is not going
to happen...!
I'm going to change it...!
Damn it...!
I'll let myself get mowed
down in her place...!
Deal with that,
you bastards...!
Things'll have to change...!
There'll be no choice...!
Okarin!
Mayuri?!
Mayuri!
I'm so... glad I was... finally
helpful... just this once.
Mayuri...
It's not... Every day...
I get... to do that...
Okarin...
No... please don't...
You can't see any stars
from here... Stay with me.
Damn it, stay with me...
Right-o. Commencing hackage.
Okabe?
What's wrong?
You gonna be
up here all day?
I told you. I want to be alone.
Yeah, I know... And I
totally respected that,
till your little woe-is-me
session took a turn
a couple hours back and
started... well... worrying me.
Out with it... Why the change of
heart about deleting the text?
You were against the idea
yourself originally, remember?
So now you're suddenly afraid
of taking some chances...?
That's what's going on?
Perhaps I've newly awakened to
my inner law-abiding citizen.
Like hell you have...
You're way too full of yourself
to be a law-abiding citizen...
Evil geniuses mock the fuzz--
I'm not an evil genius!!!
That's a bunch of childish
crap... "Hououin Kyouma...?"
Who gives a damn about him...?
He's fiction...! Haven't
you put that together...?
Well... Stop the presses,
we have a revelation.
Oh god, don't tell me
you've time leapt again?
What happened?
Hey, I've helped you get
this far, haven't I...?
Don't start holding
out on me now...
We're a team. A damn good one;
at least to hear you tell it.
We haven't made
a difference.
Suzuha... Rukako... Faris...
I asked them to sacrifice
what they cherished most,
but to what end...?
It's pointless... We haven't
been able to do a damn thing.
What are you saying?
No more...
Okabe!
Listen... I'm not an idiot...
I know you were crying...
Hashida saw it, too...
Scared the hell out of him.
Please... Tell me...
Damn it I'm trying to help!
Alright, then...
On July twenty-eighth,
Mayuri and I went to a lecture
at the Radio Building...
We... I... found you dead in
a storage closet. Stabbed...
I panicked, and not
knowing what else to do,
sent Daru a text about it
before telling anyone else...
His phone was hooked
up to the microwave and...
lo and behold, the
very first D-mail...
The very first split from
one world-line to another...
From alpha to beta, or
whatever the hell it is...
Point being, if we delete that
text from SERN's database,
we bump back to the
world-line prior to all of this.
We undo that D-mail...
You'll be...
You'll be murdered.
Don't just let it go off.
Answer it.
Mayuri?
Yep-yep!
What's up?
Well, Daru said you were
acting all strange or whatever,
so I thought maybe
I should check in...
Thank you, sweetheart, but
tell him he worries too much.
But...
I'm sorry...
It's just I was so
excited about Comima,
but, I should've paid
more attention to you...
The thing with the
ninjas got me remembering
the stories you used to tell
me about, you know, them...
Don't they have
like four leaders?
I remember Geppu, Sudachi,
Seiyuu and... Jakko?
Genbu, Suzaku,
Seiryuu and Byakko.
Those are the guys...
See though?
I do pay attention. I get
mixed up sometimes,
but I like the
Organization stuff...!
You, uh... I mean, you'd tell me
if I was a third wheel, right?
Ah, 'course you would!
Listen, I gotta go,
but if there's anything
you wanna talk about,
I'm only a phone call away!
Mayuri, wait...! I wasn't...
Go on. I'd have to be
completely tone deaf
to miss that note of
desperation in your voice,
so she must be upset.
So you should go...
Getting yourself all worked
up about what happens
to me isn't going to
solve anything right now...
Besides, there's nothing I hate
worse than being brooded over...
Find Mayuri, and do
whatever you need to do...
The longer you sit up here
and mope like some kind of
lame gargoyle, the more
pissed off I'm going to get.
Well...? Don't make
me repeat myself.
This is Mayushii...!
Actually, it's my phone,
so leave me a message--
Well?
One of the cosplayers
from her group said she
headed out quite a
while ago, actually.
I see.
I'm sorry, Gran...
Bet you came to see me
for Obon, didn't you?
I came cause I...
wanna talk about
the dreams I've
been having lately...
They're so scary...
Something really terrible
always happens to me...
I got shot in one of them;
I got hit by car
in one of them;
in another one I even got
run over by a train...!
And it always feels so real...
Like, you'd swear it actually
happened... I hate it...
I always try to scream, but I
just can't for some reason...
It's awful.
I don't know why
I keep having them.
Thing is...
Near the end, it's like,
Okarin always jumps
in and rescues me
from whatever is going on...
But, when I try
to say thank you,
it's like he can't
hear me or something...
He just stands there holding
me with this look in his eyes.
It makes me feel
really sad for him...
You can tell he's
trying not to cry,
but he's having to fight
back his tears so hard
you can tell any second
he's just gonna lose it.
I try to say I'm sorry,
but there's the whole he
can't hear me thing...
And then... I dunno.
That's the part where
I usually wake up, I guess.
Sorry, I ought to change the
subject to something nicer, huh?
We've got like a ton of new
members at the lab, now...
Kurisu, Moeka,
Ruka, Faris, Suzuha.
All super, super nice people.
It's okay, gran: you don't have
to memorize all their names.
Kurisu is super smart;
she's the only one who can
really speak Okarin's language
when he gets into that
mood of his, you know...?
It's fun to watch...
I think Mr. Mad Scientist
has finally found his match.
Sometimes... I think about
the way things used to be.
It was snowing when I came
to the lab the first time...
It was supposed to
be spring by then,
but I guess Winter
wasn't ready to go.
I'd just gotten out
of school for the day;
Okarin wasn't
even there yet.
I was cleaning the place up
when he sorta dragged
his feet through the door
the way he does sometimes...
I said "Welcome home, Okarin!"
and he just stood there.
Then he looked around
and said "good work."...
After that, I spent two
whole hours there every day,
even though we didn't
really talk all that much...
The silence wasn't
bad, though...
It was... comfortable
I guess is the best word.
It's hard to explain I dunno:
it was just a nice way
to pass the time...
I felt like the luckiest hostage
in the whole wide world!
Not too quiet for you, is it?
Nah! I like that we can just
sit here like this. It's fun.
Yes, well... Don't become
too enamored of the calm...
Domestic tranquility is a
clinically-proven
breeding ground
for all sorts of Organization-
sponsored hallucinations.
Wow. Sounds like
I'd better be careful...!
Unless, you know, they're
nice what-do-you-call-'ems...
Hallucinations.
Okey-dokey...
You think the Organization
people are really all that bad?
I miss it...
We didn't talk a lot back then,
but... it was more
than we do now...
I used to be able to
tell what was on his mind
by just looking at the
expression on his face...
That doesn't seem to be
how it works anymore...
Still, though... I can tell
he's hurting inside...
It's obvious... He looks so
tired he's about to fall over...
And I know that somehow
it's all my fault...
Whatever I've done, I'm sorry...
Ah, dang it...! I'm focusing
on the negative again, aren't I?
I don't mean to,
Gran. I really don't.
I guess... I guess I just don't
want this chapter to end yet.
Don't worry about that.
Okarin!
How'd you know
where to find me?
What kind of nonsense
question is that?
Lest we forget,
you're my hostage!
I will never allow you to
escape my dastardly clutches...
Do you hear me?
You can't keep me forever.
Do not doubt my resolve,
oh innocent one,
for I am not so
weak as to falter now.
All will be clear soon enough...
When the time is right.
Let's go.
Oo, oo! First, though, I need...
Yes, yes... You want to
buy another Oopa, I know.