That's right... This guy came up
and asked me to make him a pin.
And the sketch he showed me
looked like the pin
you came around with.
Sort of like it, or exactly like
it? A lot is riding on this!
What did this customer
of yours look like...?!
Look like...? Man,
I don't know...
I guess the dude kind
of looked like a barrel.
Like a barrel?
Did he ever give you his name?!
He didn't say...
And I didn't ask...
But he was round,
I can tell ya that much.
Round like a barrel...
Didja know "taru" is another
word for "barrel," you guys?
Taru...?!
Uh huh! I picked that up from
watching the Rai-Net anime...!
There was a barrel-monster guy,
and his real name was Taru!
I'm telling ya...
He looked just like a barrel...
Or maybe a balloon.
So he was a big guy who looked
like a barrel or a balloon?
He didn't leave you his
phone number, perchance?
Say what?!
He came to get a pin made--
not ask me out on a date.
The trail went cold, huh?
But hey... he'll go
back to pick up his pin
when it's done
being made, right?
When the vendor informed him
it would take a full week,
apparently he left
without placing an order.
I see.
I don't wanna say it, but maybe
we can't find him after all...
Yes, we can.
There is another option.
Makise will have the time-leap
machine finished by tomorrow...
Once it's operational...!
Where's Suzuha?
Huh?
She left here a
little while ago.
Don't you remember?
I'll explain later!
Dammit...! I didn't
think to ask him
what time Suzuha's
father shows up...!
Hey... can I help you?
Is that him?!
He does cut a rather spherical
figure... Wait, that hat...
Daru?!
Aw, man! Okarin?
What's gotten into you...?
Sneaking off to make a
copy of Suzuha's pin...?
Seriously, how bad's
she gonna feel
if we never find her old man...?
I figured I'd get another pin
and fake being her dad--
y'know, give her some hope.
But the hope you speak of
is based on a falsehood!
Not all lies are
created equal...
Sometimes a little white lie
can spare somebody's
feelings, y'know.
Think about the
bigger picture...!
We can locate her
real father in due time!
I'm not supposed
to tell you this,
but it's the only way you'll
stop busting my balls.
Hmm?
Her time-machine's
a one-way street...
It can't go forward...
Only back.
Once she leaves us...
she's gone for good.
How goes it?
Take a soda break... heh?
Awesome! I got me a
wicked thirst on that
only an ice-cold
diet soda can quench...!
It's like you read
my mind, man!
Well? Do you think
you can get it working?
Should have it done by tomorrow.
Check this guy out!
We're gonna have time to spare!
Daru's a cheetah when
it comes to tech jobs...
I told you not to judge
a book by its cover.
Huh? Wait, you did?
I don't remember that.
Anyway, ol' Daru
here's so unassuming,
I'd have never known
he was such a bad-ass.
So I guess you're right, Okabe.
Wanna hop in and
lend a hand, Suzuha...?
The heat in the time-machine
might be oppressive,
but it's nothing
that can't be fixed
by stripping down to
our unmentionables...
Why're you such a creeper?!
Wow, Suzuha and Daru make
a pretty good match, huh!
Listen... There's
something I need to say,
and the chance might
not come up later, so...
Thanks so much...
You guys have really
gone to bat for me.
When I first came to this time,
I didn't know a single
person around here, you know?
This place might be
a walk in the park
compared to where I'm from...
but to me, it was
still as scary as hell.
But now, just get a load of
all the awesome people here
that I can call friend...
Traveling back to this
period was a good idea...
This was... the most fun
I've ever had, y'know?
I'm glad I got this
time to be with you guys,
even if it wasn't for long...
Being a member of the Future
Gadget Lab... it was nice.
Once she leaves us...
she's gone for good.
It's up to you now--you're
the only chance we've got--
I promise you I'll do it!
Suzuha, I'll keep the world
exactly the way it is right now!
Okabe, how did you...?
Do you...
Do you regret... the time
you've spent with us...?
If you could never
see us again...
would you come to regret having
known us in the first place...?
I mean, were
we worth it...?
I get it...
Daru told you, didn't he?
He's worried... And
he's not the only one.
I can't not go!
Changing the future
was my dad's life work,
and now it's mine.
This is your future
we're talking about, too!
How can you just maroon
yourself in the past?!
I'm not headed to some
gulag. It's the '70s.
Long as I can make friends
half as cool as you guys,
I think I'll be alright
wherever I end up.
Here goes nothing...!
I think you're good to go now,
but if you wanna double-check,
then knock yourself out.
All systems are go! I can't
believe you got it working!
Wouldn't kill ya to smile...!
Hey, you just fixed
a time-machine!
Cheer up...! No one else
on Earth can say that!
Okay, what part of
'75, you guys...?
Oh, I could go in the summer;
the weather'd probably
be pretty nice.
What do you think, Daru?
Nah, I'd aim a bit earlier.
If you arrive just as the
cherry blossoms are blooming,
more folks'll be out and about.
Better for making
friends, you know?
Wow, good thinking!
Earlier it is!
"FG204...?"
Hey, Suzuha!
Huh?
What's up?
What does that mean?
I should have
introduced you sooner.
That's the time-machine's name.
My dad came up with it.
What's my bike doing here?
Take the tires off and it's
small enough to bring along.
We knew how much you
liked the darn thing.
i'll treasure it.
Thanks, you guys.
I got it...!
Detective Mayuri figured
out who your father is,
Suzuha--and just in
the nick of time!
What?!
What's better... you
could reach out right now
and give your dad
a great big hug!
Right... now...?!
See, I was wearing
my thinking cap...
...and, I suddenly realized why
you two make such a good match.
It isn't just 'cause
you're friends,
'cause we're your
friends, too...
It's because you
two are family!
Wait...! Are you saying...?!
Suzuha's long-lost father...
...is Daru!
Huh...?! Me??
That isn't the sort of thing
you joke about, Mayuri...!
As if any self-respecting
woman would ever actually--
Hey! No need to be mean!
This is a big deal!
Please tell me you've got
more than to go off of...!
Well, remember how I said that
"barrel" and taru were the same?
Taru... Itaru... There ya go!
That's your reason...?!
Word-play does not
establish fatherhood!
Yeah but, what about
that rebel group Suzuha
is part of in the
future, Okarin...?
It was founded by you and
Barrel Titor, wasn't it?
And... the only other guy
who knows about all the
time-machine stuff you're
doing in Akihabara in 2010...
and your Reading
Stoner thing--
Reading Steiner.
Sure...
Well, the only guy who'd
know about those is
Daru, right...? So...
But the very best clue that I
found was right under our noses!
What, the
time-machine's name...?
Yup--FG204.
FG like Future Gadget, you see?!
I... suppose it
could be, but...!
Check out the rest...!
Does that remind
anyone of anything?
Kay, it says Future Gadget
Two Hundred and Four,
Second Edition, version
two-point-three-one!
That padded naming style...
You're my dad...?
Uh... guess you gotta call
me big daddy from now on, huh?
Are you seriously gonna
make even this moment pervy?
You're my dad.
Yeah, I... guess I am.
I went back... Just
like you wanted, Dad...
And I found you...
I found you with the
time-machine you built...
Yeah.
You never got the
chance to fix the world.
But I'm gonna finish
what you started!
And I'm gonna make
you proud of me.
That's... gonna
be kinda tough...
'Cause I already
am proud of you.
I have to know...
Your Mother.
Was she smokin' hot?
Short, baby-faced, huge
rack--am I in the ballpark?
I'm keeping that one to myself!
Well... I guess it's time...
Right.
I know you're going really far,
but please don't
forget about us!
You be careful.
Thanks--you, too.
That IBN 5100 is as good
as mine--you'll see...!
I'll make sure it gets to
you guys in one piece, K?
I won't see it, but...
make it a good future, yeah?
The next time you guys see me,
I'll be a little old lady.
You better recognize me
when I'm 35 years older!
Suzuha!
Suzuha...! I promise you...
we're gonna meet again...!
Things might get rough, but
you gotta hang in there...!
You gotta be strong!
...for your dad...
This just in: The rogue
satellite on the roof
of the Radio Building in
Akihabara has disappeared.
Hey... this word on the pin...
Call me crazy, but I think
it's just our initials...
O's Okabe... H is for
Hashida, S for Shina...
Ah! Then the M's
gotta stand for Makise,
and the A is for Amane! Right?
Cool--it's a lab member pin!
Guess we should
get some made, huh?
Totally!
What's that look for?
Why aren't we seeing
any difference
in the numbers on
the Divergence Meter.
Maybe they can't change
until she brings us the
IBN 5100 in the present.
If I did the math right,
Suzuha's 54 years old by now...
Man, that's a trip, that means
I'm three decades younger
than my own daughter...
Probably has grandkids, too,
she's old enough, you know.
Whoa. Hold the phone...
You mean I might get to
meet my own great-grandkids
while I'm still young
enough to enjoy 'em?!
You better spoil 'em like crazy!
That's what
great-grandpas are for!
Suzuha!
Mr. Braun...?!
A letter?
Hashida... Suzu...?!
D'you really think
it's from her?!
Wait a sec! Why'd he
bring it up to us?
That letter is from a
woman who did me a favor,
once upon a time...
She told me to pass it along to
you, but only on this exact day.
This woman...
where is she now...?
A better place.
She passed on ten years ago.
"Dear Okabe... This is your
very old friend... Suzuha..."
"In 2010, I've only been
gone for a matter of hours."
"I'm writing from
the year 2000...
a decade before I left...
I need to tell you..."
"...that I failed my mission."
"I failed... I failed...
I failed... I failed...
I failed..."
"I only had to do one
thing and I failed...
I failed... I failed...!"
"I only remembered the truth
of who I am a year ago...
All that wasted time..."
"Everything that happened
before 1975 was just... gone."
"When I made the jump,
there was a critical failure...
Something in the machine
was still broken..."
"Please tell Dad not
to blame himself...
The fault was all mine!"
"I should've just gone straight
back to 1975, like he wanted...
instead of risking everything
with a stop in 2010!"
"God, how could
I have been so selfish...?!"
"The future's doomed
because of me!"
"I've never even
seen an IBN 5100..."
"I'm sorry... I'm sorry...!"
"I forgot... about my
mission... my duty..."
"I lived an easy life, with
my head in the goddamn sand...!"
Please...! Please forgive me!"
"Dear Okabe... when I couldn't
find my dad that one evening,
you stopped me from giving
up and heading to 1975."
"So I stayed... and the
storm that night damaged
the time-machine in
ways we never found."
"If you can turn back time...
I ask that you not
stop me that night."
"My life was..."
"...a waste."
Mr. Braun.
Huh...? Whaddya want? I'm
trying to call it a day here.
I don't mean to pry, but...
can you tell me how
Hashida Suzu died?
Why the hell do you care?
Please sir, this is important!
I'll beg if I have to...!
I need to know what
happened to her...!
All I'm asking for
is some closure...!
If this is you
just being nosy,
I'll wring your neck
like a chicken...
But I'll bite--how'd
a kid like you know
a lady who died in 2000?
We were...
...old friends...
Very old friends...
But I remember the
time we spent together...
A lifetime ago, but it
feels like yesterday ...!
Talkin' about the whole
thing still eats at me...
She killed herself.
Hanged herself in
her house one day.
I should've seen it coming.
She'd been off for about a
year... Y'know... mentally.
She was so sunny
and all before...
Guess I thought
she'd get through it.
It's my fault...
Her time-machine never
would have malfunctioned
if I hadn't prevented her
from leaving that night
the way she intended to.
If I hadn't messaged
myself to follow her,
she could have
traveled back to 1975
with the memory of what
she had to do intact!
You didn't know...
What are you doing...?!
Hey! Talk to me!
I can't let her die...
Not again...!
Please don't send
another one, Okarin...!
If you press that button,
it's like none of
this was ever real!
I have to...
Don't you see what'll happen?
She'll never know who her father
was if you send that message!
I have to!
I won't see it, but...
make it a good future, yeah?
Okarin!
Huh...? What are you looking at?
"Hashida Suzu," huh...?
I wasn't expecting that...
So... I'm assuming
you knew her?
Yeah... And she's
been well... I hope...?
Passed away 'bout ten
years ago, give or take...
She was real good
to me, Suzu was...
Wish I could've done something
to help her there at the end...
Killed herself... Didn't she.
The hell...?! She got
sick and died, you freak!
I lived with her,
so I would know...!
"Killed herself" my ass...!
That bicycle...!
It's a beaut...
Suzu loved the hell
outta that bike--
she'd ride it any
chance she got.
I don't have the
heart to scrap it...
so it's been sitting
out here ever since.
We were just neighbors
at first. "Hi."
"How ya doin'?"
Y'know... But later,
when my house burned down
along with all my stuff...
...she rented one of
her rooms out to me.
Charged me next to nothing,
and only accepted
that because I insisted.
Did she have a family,
or... was it just her?
I don't think she
ever got married,
if that's what you mean...
She was a rare bird, that one.
Y'know, I asked her once...
"Why are you being so good to a
fella who isn't nothing to ya?"
She just smiled that easy
smile of hers, and said...
"Everybody needs a hand
at some point or another.
That's how life works...
Just make sure you're ready
to lend a hand yourself
when your number comes up."
Oh, yeah... Gimmie a sec.
This... thing was
her prized possession.
Any idea what those
numbers are about?
Near the end, when
she was bedridden,
she would just gaze at it...
"Is this the number from before,
or the number from after?"
she'd murmur to
herself, always asking
"Did I change it, or
was it all for nothing?
I can't be sure."...
It was constantly on her mind.
The divergence number...
it went up...
It's higher... but it's
still under one percent...
The train on the outside loop
will be arriving momentarily...
For your safety, please
remain behind the yellow line.
But that means... nobody's
called in a bomb-threat!
Mayuri!
Oh no...!
Huh?
You feeling okay?
Yeah... I'm fine.
Oh, hey... Mayuri's phone
was going nuts a bit earlier.
Sorry if that was you, man...
I hollered for her to
wake up, y'know, but no dice.
Suzuha... did we change
the world enough...?
Is Mayuri... going to live...?