Makise... Kurisu...!
Hey, sorry, I tried
knocking but no one came.
But... How did
you ferret us out?
I asked Hashida for
the street address...
Though I gotta admit,
I was expecting less of a frat
pad and more of an actual lab...
Idiot...! You betrayed me
to this nattering vixen?!
Huh?
It's okay, you
were ill-prepared
to deal with a
three-dimensional woman...!
Well, hah! the battle for
Daru's soul is not over!
I'm onto you... Mata Hari!
Could you please tell
him I'm not a spy?
My telling him so's not
gonna do you very much good.
We are undone!
The Organization's
finally worked
an agent into our
sanctum sanctorum...!
What...?!
Our present calamity can't
be the choice of Stein's Gate!
What in the hell
is a Stein's Gate?
It's just a phrase he's partial
to. It doesn't mean anything.
Sure yeah... Why would I expect
anything he says to make sense?
Off with the boots!
Huh? Oh! Sorry. Guess I spent
too much time in the States...
I'm Makise Kurisu... Might as
well do it official-like, huh?
What's the matter...?
Are you one of those
Japanese guys
who shakes hands
like a dead fish?
Don't wet yourself.
They've probably taught you
twenty ways to kill a man...
Can you blame me for not
jumping headlong into oblivion?
Hey, where d'you
think you're going?!
Uh, inside...?
I came here to find
out why you were
so surprised to
see me "alive"...
or if that was just
your clever excuse
to go poking around in my coat.
And that...
The rest are still
attached to it...
Doesn't look faked...
She's packing a doomsday device!
Don't you take your eyes
off her for a nanosecond!
Sure thing, boss.
Huh... Got tweezers?
No!
Fine.
Viscous consistency...
Flavor...Yuck... Not good.
Sad zombie!
Eating that in lieu
of brain matter!
I'd have given you a banana!
You pervert...! Jeez...
You just wanna
watch me eat a banana.
Nuh uh!
Isn't it enough that
you were groping me
practically the moment we met?
I don't mean to
interrupt anything, but...
What?
You know how you said,
"You just wanna watch me eat
a banana" a second ago...?
Could you, like,
repeat that for me...?
Only this time
whisper it a little bit?
Why would I do that?
What's the problem? It's a
perfectly innocuous request!
Unless--no, that
would be impossible!
Something that nasty
wouldn't occur to you...!
What sprang to mind?!
We're all dying to know!
You know damn
well what I thought
'cause you thought it first!
Awesome.
No, it's not!
Oooooh, methinks the lady
with the fruit fixation
doth protest too muuuch!
I don't have a
fixation...! Listen...
While I'd love to run
screaming to the cops
about the pair of you perverts,
I'm going to hold off for now.
"For now," huh?
The you-know-what
on the table...
Don't even start.
The microwave did that, right?
That's top-secret--avert
your eyes, woman...!
Future Gadget numero 8 is
our laboratory's most
diabolical weapon!
She's pretty smart, man.
No point playing keep-away
if she can tell us
how the thing works.
Yeah--smart and evil--!
By the time you
and me figure it out,
we're gonna have
flying cars and junk!
But everything in the
Future Gadget Lab
is for members' eyes-only!
You there! "Christina,"
you said your name was?
Yeah. Never said that.
I will divulge its secrets
to you if, and only if...!
Firstly...!
You must join our sacred
brotherhood of anarchic science,
the Future Gadget Laboratory.
You're really going to
make me join your stupid lab
to look at your microwave?
I mean, I guess I could,
but I'm headed back home to the
United States in August, so...
Your membership is provisional.
Now, secondly...
You do not run screaming to the
cops about us being perverts!
Take it or leave it!
Hey, if you ever get
burned out on science,
you'd be one hell of a
lawyer, my friend... Serious!
You rule at the smooth-talk!
Thank you, Daru!
Now, you've no qualms about
my generous conditions, right?
Generous to you, maybe.
Me... I'm one banana comment
away from fight-or-flight.
You haven't said
no, Christina...
That isn't my name, you nut-job!
Oh, right! You're the Zombie!
How would you like it...
Hououin Carcinoma!
Kyoma...! watch your
tongue, banana-mouth!
In the movies, this is
when you two'd get busy.
Give it a rest, perv!
Okay, I accept...
On one condition, though,
you need to give it a rest with
all the fruit-based innuendo...
I wouldn't want to have to start
reaching for the pepper-spray.
Ah, sweet victory.
I hereby nomenclate you
Lab Member Double-O Four!
Also known as Chrrrristina!
No I am not!
"When you're on
a chicken bender,
grab a box of chicken
tenders! Bock-bock-ba-gock!"
Saying it's a teleporter
doesn't make it so.
You can't just go
with your first thought.
I suppose you'd
have us go with yours?
A banana moved a couple of feet.
I'm just saying, I think
"teleporter" is premature.
Ooh, we have a guest!
A pleasure to meet you...
I'm Makise Kurisu...
I hope my being here
didn't startle you.
I'm Shiina Mayuri.
Are you a member of the lab?
I just became one, myself.
Seriously?
Yup.
Ah!! A girl... I won't
be the only one?!
Uh... is it that big of a deal?
Super! Big! Deal...!
You're the only girl
who's ever been up here
other than me,
can you believe it?
Ya don't say.
Nice to meetcha!
Thank you...! And likewise!
What the deuce?!
What's up?
There was electrical discharge!
What...?! Why didn't you
tell me about that sooner...?!
Give me all of the
relevant data you have!
Well... lightning came
out of the microwave...
Yeah. That...
pretty much covers it.
When, exactly?
Yesterday around noon, I think.
You tore outta here
after they showed
that crashed satellite on TV...
so I guinea-pigged
my phone onto it.
When I texted from
the Radio Building...
you're telling me the
Phone Wave (Real Name TBA)
was actually wired
in to your cell-phone?
That nutty one about Makise
getting eighty-sixed...?
You fired that thing
off to me last week!
The hell I did...! I sent
it yesterday...! At noon...!
Where'd it go?! It should
be right here, dammit...!
What was the microwave
doing when it got zapped?
I was running some tests on it.
Tryin' ta see if I could get
the turntable to go
counterclockwise.
We should try to recreate
those same conditions.
Mayuri, will your
chicken tenders
heed the call of science?!
Yes!
Chicken tenders taste best
when you eat them with friends!
Why are we putting those
things in there, again?
I want to see if superfluous
material affects the end result.
Engage.
Now then... send
me a text, assistant.
Okay, first of all,
I am not your assistant...
And even if I were,
I don't know your phone number.
So hard to find
good help... Daru.
Your phone will
have to suffice.
Whaddaya want it to say?
How about...
"Christina... is a pervert."
Don't go pushing
your luck, jerkwad.
How about I just
split the difference...?
"Okarin is a pervert."
Whaddya think?
What?!
Attaboy...! Good thinking!
Firing torpedoes, Captain!
And now... we play
the waiting game...
I betcha those tenders
are nice and hot.
Mayuri! No!
Huh?
You all right...?!
Mm-hm...
Suck it, A.C.!
What just happened?
Electromagnetic pulse...?
Don't be an idiot...
We're talking about a
microwave you probably bought
secondhand at some pawn
shop, not a hydrogen bomb.
Ahh! My chickies
are charcoal...!
They'll never be
tender again...!
What're we gonna do about
that hole in the floor?
Mr. Braun's gonna
burst a blood-vessel.
Well?
Jackpot...
Received July 24th...
at 5:30 p.m....!
It really went back in time...!
Did you figure something out?
"Something?"
More like everything...!
My sterling brain has
sliced through this riddle
in one fell swoop!
Seriously?
Just as the banana has returned
to the bunch from
whence it was taken...
this text has jumped
five days into the past!
But that... would mean...!
Yes--exactly! This humble
kitchen appliance is...!
...a time machine!
Thirteen... new text
messages...? Who's S.F....?
Ah, yes.
That shrinking violet
I christened "Shining Finger."
Should've called her
"Hyperactive Finger"...
"Text me right away"
"Hey, are you asleep yet?"
"How long are you gonna
sleep d'you think?"
Daru...
You fancy a
mid-morning walk...?
What's wrong?
We burned the
midnight oil for nothing...
I'm getting' a
little low on morale.
Plus my 2D harem hates
it when I neglect 'em.
Why aren't they turning
into gel-nanas anymore?
Beats me...
How come we can't send
any more texts back in time?
Maybe we should pick
Makise's brain again...
The S.S. Christina has sailed.
No...! But that's impossible...!
And that was the
last we saw of her.
Why'd she get so freaked out?
Hmm? What'm I looking at?
Just the LHC.
Huh?
Large Hadron Collider.
SERN's particle accelerator.
Ain't she a thing o' beauty...?
SERN maintains a strict monopoly
on the time machine market.
Titor... He mentioned them.
That guy... the one you
were goin' on about...?
Suddenly there's people talking
about him all over the internet.
What does it stand for?!
Huh...?!
In his posts, John Titor says
that SERN completes a
working time machine by 2034...
Too early for crazy-talk...
Just tell me...!
What does it stand for?!
Get off my jock
and I'll tell ya!
SERN's full name is
the European Organization
in Nuclear Research.
They're based outside Geneva.
Their big thing is
particle physics research,
hence the name.
And rightly so--check out the
hardware these cats are packing.
The Low Energy Antiproton Ring,
the Proton Synchrotron Booster,
the Large Electron-Positron
Collider,
and the baddest mama-jama...!
The world's largest
particle accelerator!
The Large Hadron Collider!
There were even
rumors going 'round
that the LHC could
produce micro black holes.
If anything could, that'd be it.
Black holes, you say, huh?
Daru.
Yuh huh?
Is there or isn't there a
prevalent school of thought
that posits time-travel is
possible through the creation
and exploitation of
miniature black holes?
Yeah... there is...
but Makise's lecture
pretty much let the daylight
through that one...
She said it's impossible
to create black holes
to begin with.
You just told me maybe
the LHC could do it...!
Who's to say they haven't--?!
Oh yeah...!
Nah ... SERN told everybody
they struck out, man.
Please, as though I would just
blithely take their word for it.
It's me.
Heh. He's so naïve. I know.
El... Psy... Congroo.
Wanna remind me what
windmill we're tilting at now?
At this juncture, Daru,
we've but one course of action.
Go visit Faris at the maid café!
Wrong!
Don't make me fight
this fight alone!
I need your exemplary
'leet skills, Hack!
Stop. And don't
talk nerd to me.
You know what must be done.
No and I don't
want to hear this.
We hack into SERN.
Simple.
You're kidding...
Tell me you're kidding.
Break into their network,
and gather intel on
their time-travel program.
Your prowess with a keyboard
will determine whether
the Phone Wave (Real Name TBA)
slips the bonds of time,
or is condemned to a
life of desultory heating.
Don't get pissy
if it doesn't work!
Here ya go. Two beef bowls.
Huh?
That'll be 800 yen.
Okariiiiin!
Hard at work, I see.
You know it. The shop
doesn't get any customers.
I'm dying of boredom.
You should have gotten
work at a bike store.
'Fess up... What kind of hijinks
are you guys getting up to?
With a name like "Future Gadget
Laboratory," it's gotta be--
Who divulged that name?!
Uh...
Ah ha, well, if
you know that much,
I suppose you can
handle the truth...
We've taken up arms against
a so-called "benign" group
that fancies itself a
shadow government.
We're just about to
fire the first shot
in a vicious
cyber-war, in fact.
Wow, that sounds
pretty hardcore!
And the group you're
talking about, it's SERN, yeah?
How do you know that?!
My bad... See, I... I heard
you going on about it...
I just... get so...
bored down here,
and voices carry, you know?
So you admit to
spying on us, then?!
Not my fault I got
good ears. Heh...
Ahhh, but don't worry about it!
Your secret is safe with me!
Not again...
What is it?
The daily death report?
The daily what now?
Oh, nothing... It's
a line from a show.
Just a retro-PC fan-girl...
She wants me to help
her find an IBN 5100.
IBN?
So you've heard of it!
Uh... Kinda... maybe...
Those keen ears of yours?
Hey, c'mon--cut me some slack!
He was talking
about 'em online...
Y'know, that time-traveler dude.
"John Titor," or whatever...
Titor was?!
Yeah, I read all about it on
some web-forum or other...
He was saying something
like the IBN 5100
was built before PCs
were using BASIC...
so it can read IBN's
proprietary programming code,
which no other PC can--
Are you sure?!
Yeah...
Back when he first showed up
on the boards in
2000, didn't Titor...?
It's curious...
All of you seem to
embrace a very...
entrenched concept of time.
Contrary to your beliefs,
time is not a river flowing
from past to future in
an inexorable current.
For example,
let's say I go back in time and
kill somebody we'll call "A."
Doing so will lead
to an alteration
of what is known as the
"divergence number"...
and the world line will
shift to a universe without A.
When a world line shifts,
people's memories are
changed accordingly...
So... memories of the world
in which A continued
to exist are nullified...
Overwritten with
memories of a world line
in which his life was
cut short by my actions.
Please explain.
How exactly does SERN,
a benign research organization,
end up becoming a
tyrannical oligarchy?
Kind of hard to understand.
SERN is not so benign as
they would have you believe.
For example,
they have already succeeded in
producing miniature black holes.
Perhaps the easiest way
to characterize my future
is a return to 18th-century
living standards under
a global framework
of communism.
In 2036, SERN controls most
of the world's technology
and scientific knowledge.
And you require an
IBN 5100 to prevent
this future of yours
from occurring, I assume?
That is correct.
The IBN 5100's
singular abilities
are needed to halt
SERN's ambitions.
If memory serves, you
said much the same thing
in your posts when
you appeared in 2000.
When I appeared
in 2000, you say?
As I've stated before,
I have never had occasion
to travel to the year 2000.
However, there's
always the possibility
that you remember me
from another world line.
I'm intrigued.
I would very much like to
speak with you at some point.
This is my e-mail address...
If you contact me, I will reply.
Almost there, Daru...
C'mon, you can do this...
Just ferret out the SQL
database table's configuration
and start decrypting
like a mo'fo'. Yeah.
G'morning!
Oh, hey Mayuri.
What're you up to
this glorious morn?
Since you stayed up
two nights in a row,
I thought you'd like
some tasty snacks. Yum!
Ooo! Canned oden stew!
Once again, your contribution
to the cause is inspiring.
I can't treat often,
but today's special...
See, I needed to get some of
these Rai-Net sausages, anyway.
They're giving away a free oopa
with every single box you buy!
Heh. You and your oopas.
No oopas come with your
stew, but it's still tasty!
Daru and Kurisu get their
own cans too, so no sharing!
Ugh... The fail is strong
with this one...!
He didn't even hear me, did he?
There's nothing sadder
than a hackaholic, Mayuri.
Keep going, Hack! You can do it!
We believe in you 100 percent!
Now ya got her saying it!
It isn't nice to go snooping
around in other people's stuff.
We have to bring
SERN's inequities to light.
Yeah, I know... but...
I think maybe Kurisu ran away
'cause she didn't think
it was very nice, either.
Whatever reason she
had for leaving the lab,
I can guarantee you
the hacking wasn't it.
I hope she comes
back some day...
I liked her a whole lot.
Huh...? How come?
I'd like to exchange this
fish-cake for a beef strip.
Yeah...? Can I trade
for a quail egg instead?
Not a chance.
Quail eggs are my second
favorite, after the beef strips.
They're my first favorite.
Pretty please?
How about a fish-tube?
They're pretty good.
I guess that's better
than a beef strip.
It's a pleasure doing
business with you, madam.
'Kay! One beef strip,
coming up...Where'd it--?
Already took it.
Huh...?! But when'd you...?
Wow...
Much obliged, Mayuri.
Jackpooooot!
In your face...!
In your face, SERN!
All your base
are belong to me!
You have no
chance--make your time!
Yeah...! Fake user ID get!
You're inside?!
Hashida Daru for the win!
I don't know what you did,
but I'm really proud of you.
Now don't get too excited,
I did hack our way in--
but there are limits to what
we can see without an admin ID,
and that ain't gonna happen...
Like when an H-game just
shows you the boobs, ya know?
You're so naughty, Daru!
What'd you find?
A couple e-mails so far,
but the day's still young.
Quite a bit of text.
Should we hard copy for safety?
Nah, it's okay.
I've got it locked in.
Experiment report...
February 9...
Spare me the dramatic
reenactment, please.
Suit yourself... Okay...
"The LHC is performing
as intended.
It is a fickle device,
to be sure,
but the last month's work has
gone forward without a hitch."
What's he talking about?
What about the time machine?!
Somebody must have discussed
it in one of these messages!
Let's give it a whirl...
"Time machine" is
coming up a goose egg...
but the term
"Z-Program" was used
about 100 times
in the past month.
Okay... "Z-Program
Experiment Report 137"...
"As the goal of generating
miniature black holes
has already been met,
the contents of this
report have been deleted."
Whoa.
They were successful...!
It looks that way...
But they told everybody those
experiments totally bombed...!
Read the next one!
"Outcome of trial..."
"Human is dead... Mismatch."
Human is dead.
Uh-huh...
Someone...
...died?