We're now on day five of the
mysterious satellite incident
here at the downtown
Radio Building...
Throngs of onlookers continue
to flock in the street below
in hopes of catching
a firsthand glimpse,
and as no country has
yet come forward to
claim the offending object,
it's anyone's guess when life
here will return to normal.
Can we have a
moment of your time?
You're, here to get a look
at the satellite I assume, yes?
Could you tell our viewers at
home where you've traveled from?
Wowza! Are you kidding?
It's awesome!
This, like, your
first beef bowl?
Yep! And I gotta say: the
hype doesn't do 'em justice!
Yes, well, you really ought to
try it with raw egg sometime...
That is, of course,
once you've mastered
this unwarrior-like
phobia of eating out alone.
Daru and I only dine
together out of convenience,
you understand.
You're more than welcome to
join us whenever you'd like...
Hey! It's comin' back to me...
The last time we came here,
you totally skipped out
and left me with the check!
I do concede that as
a distinct possibility.
Try a distinct
damn right-ability!
Where're my
greenbacks, Bogart?!
Not the day to bark up
that tree, I'm afraid...
It's me.
Kindly make the aforementioned
monetary transfers
into my Swiss bank
account, if you would...
That one, yes...
Wait, what?
The Organization
is playing havoc...
Please. No. Cell-phones.
Er, does it count if the
conversation's all in his head?
Too-too-roo!
I didn't know you were
part of the group now.
Oh, I was just on the
ol' lunch break, you know...
You'd should've
come around earlier,
it would have been a party.
I propose we do this
again tomorrow, all of us.
Okarin's treat.
No no no. Don't put me on hold!
Crisis or not,
it can't take the banks a full
week to straggle back online...!
Cool, the gang's all here!
Double-O Four.
Well-rested, I trust?
Don't start with
that crap again.
Hey. I hate to break
up your meeting...
but your lunch break
ended five minutes ago.
What's that about?
Round table?
Yep.
That like a thing...?
A lab member
pow-wow, indeed.
You make it sound like
we do 'em all the time.
Only table I see
here is rectangular.
Ugh. I don't mean it literally;
"round table" is simply
a figure of speech;
meant to evoke camaraderie--
Thank you. I'm quite
familiar with the expression.
I'm just never sure whether you
mean things literally or not.
I think it sounds sweet
even if it is rectangular.
Thank you...
You're welcome...!
So let's start...
Who's gonna bring
the "camaraderie"?
Yeah, what now, chief?
You pull a sword from a stone?
I'd like to point out
that as a temporary member
I shouldn't be
eligible to attend.
Oh my goodness... Fine!
I grant you special
privileges... Moving on.
Our needs must be to apprise
Mayuri of notre dilemme.
Uh oh. What's that?
In short, my minions,
if we intend
to nip SERN's odious design
in the proverbial bud,
perfecting the Phone
Wave (Real Name TBA)'s
incipient functionality
is absolutely paramount.
Awww, you use so many big words
the little ones around them
don't make sense either.
Let me put it this way then,
SERN is very, very bad.
'Kay, but what do you mean
by perfecting it, though?
I mean...
We already sent texts back in
time, what else do you think--?
True, but in point of fact,
we've only done so twice!
Flying blind, I might add. No.
We have to look for patterns.
Well then, we know
from the last experiment
it only seems to work when
there's an electrical discharge.
Eureka!
Flash of inspiration?
No, it's just that "Mail From
the Past" is too inelegant...
If we expect to be inspired
we must first christen
the phenomena
with a decent name.
How 'bout...
Cart before the horse?
Not helpful!
Continue to mock me,
and my wrath shall
hamme--
Please.
You'd get sidetracked thinking
up a name for a screwdriver.
Excuse me! Prepare to
eat your words, nay-sayer.
I've already plucked a name
for the facts in question,
as if from thin air!
We shall call it:
Kyouma's Nostalgia Drive!
I, propose referring
to it as KND for short.
Catchy anagrams are
far more marketable--
Sounds like a fast food chain.
Duly noted, temporary assistant!
Now if you'll just let...
I say we have a
show of hands...
Who here is good with
"Kyouma's Nostalgia Drive?"
Come on! Neither of you?!
Sorry, I agree with her.
It's not a bad name...
But even when you don't
use the letters it makes
me think of a charity.
Yeah. 'sides,
"Kyouma"? Nice try.
In the interest of keeping
it cute and simple...
Since it goes against
the flow of time,
why not call it
"contrary-mail."
I don't get it.
You have a lot to
learn about "cute."
Why are we arguing
when it should clearly be "The
Mail That Leapt Through Time"?
Because we're not entering
it into a film festival.
Now you're just being a brat.
At least my idea
doesn't make you
wanna order a bucket
of chicken wings!
Balance, man! We need
romance and concision!
Then I'll squish it to
"Time Leaper..."
Except that now we don't
know what's leaping, do we?
Maybe we could work
"banana" in there somewhere?
Ah! Can you
imagine our logo?!
Too-too-roo!
Ha...! Just wait till you
get a load of this one...!
We call it...
"Flux Mail Capacitor."
Are we implying that it
runs on plutonium now?
Ooo! Ooo!
"DeLorean Mail"...!
That doesn't make sense.
Close enough...
Though, if we go with that,
I'd suggest we
shorten it to "D-Mail."
Oh! That's a good one!
Great. We can move on. Finally.
We now begin our experiments
with D-Mail (Real Name TBA)...
Drop the TBA. We've got it.
Fine. I dub this
Operation Wyrd--
You can drop that, too.
I'd like to get
back to the whole
"we don't have a clue
what's happening" issue.
I mean, we're pretty sure the
electrical surges are related,
but that's about it.
Precisely what we've gathered
here to establish, Hack...
Thanks to my genius, however,
we're not shooting in the dark.
You, dear cohorts,
have overlooked
the simplest yet most
crucial condition involved...
To wit: Time!
The first D-Mail made
its apparent leap backward
between noon and one o'clock;
the second at approximately
six in the evening.
Thus... if we conduct
our experiments
so that the same
windows are observed,
success is a
strong likelihood.
Dude. If it were that easy
you think we'd be the
ones to discover it?
If you can do
better I'm all ears.
Mayuri! Banana me!
We're running kind of
low on the test subjects...
We could just use
something else, couldn't we?
Maybe a cucumber...
Hack! This is hardly
the time... No.
The effect on bananas
classifies as a known.
So, if you'd be so good as
to insert what we have left...
"Insert..."
Oh, grow up...! I swear...
I'm sorry, sweetie...
Look, I promise to
buy you some more
as soon as we're done here.
Aw, really...?!
These two guys never
buy me anything.
It's gonna be awesome having
you around the lab, I can tell!
Oww!
Please... Enough
with the show-boating.
Shut up.
Leave my friend alone, ouchies.
Oh, it's not that bad.
Put away the tea
set, Princess Ow.
There's work to do.
Send me a text.
Okay, okay.
Minute thirty
good for the timer?
Yes... Commence Operation Wyrd!
Now!
Yes... That's it!
Show me what you've got!
The fruit is where?!
It's a gel-nana, it worked!
Whoa...
Just as I hypothesized!
Time of day is an
essential component
in how the D-Mail system works!
I am a genius!
Nice job, Okabe.
I, was kind of inclined to
doubt you at first, but...
Forgiven...
It is quite enough to see that
you are appropriately
awed by my intellect.
Whatever. Did you get the text?
Indeed... Five days ago,
to be exact.
Yeah, but there's two.
Did you send another one?
Nuh-uh. Just the one.
Interesting. It's been split up.
I'm not familiar
with this vernacular.
In America it's a compliment.
You know, now
that I think about it,
your D-mail to me the other
day was all broken up, too.
Part of it was cut off,
as a matter of fact.
And 'course it popped
up five days earlier...
I know, right? Probably
some physical... law...
Wait that would mean
my head's full of air...
There is no way
that's a compliment!
How are you just
now getting that?
That vile little minx and her
infernal insults...! Blast!
Are you stocking up
for the end of times...?
Ramen and one-- one --bag
of paraffin chocolate
is more than enough.
It looks like you're
amping up for a bender.
What, a guy can't celebrate
a successful experiment?
Put em back, lard silo.
Screw. You.
My god...
I was so excited about our
success I neglected to weigh
the reality of what
we've uncovered here...
Mayuri's knee deep
in this, too...
Why on earth did I tell her?
Well, if it isn't my old
pen pal Shining Finger.
Yes, hi.
What is wrong with you?
I'm right here.
Where... where's your phone?
Well, I'd tell you
if you were authorized
to be briefed on the
epoch-ushering experiment
it is currently central to...
Ready when you are.
Um, boss...?
Who's this spank worthy--
Er, I mean, totally respectable
young meatspace angel
with the knock-out
ass in front of me?
How rude of me.
Daru, meet Kiryuu Moeka,
a.k.a. Shining Finger.
Hello there, my lovely lady...
And just like that,
a man's drop-kicked
back into the shady underworld
of all-night RPGs...
Yo...! Check it...!
You party people bringin'
the ruckus or what?
In a manner of speaking.
Our researches will indeed
bring, as you say, the--
Yeah, that's real
crunk and all, but...
Papa Bald Cap is seriously
pissed off at you guys...
Says the vibrations from your
floor are givin' him migraines.
"You want your rent to give
you a damn migraine?!"...
I can't do the voice,
but you get it.
Damn it all...! Hack!
Run upstairs and tell the girls
to suspend all experimentation.
I'll try and
sweet-talk the cur.
Roger. I'm on top of it...
good luck not getting evicted.
Is Makise Kurisu
still up there?
Huh? She is.
But I don't understand
what that could
possibly mean to you...
Why were you giving
her the evil eye...?
What happened in your past?
Nothing happened in the past.
I see it now:
you were turtle fishing
and she carelessly let
slip through her fingers
the finest red-eared
slider ever--
Stop it! I'd never
seen her before!
Why are you here
gabbin' with me anyway?
Shouldn't you be groveling?
I don't know what
you're doing up there
and I don't wanna know...
But if it involves an elephant,
you're in breach of your lease.
Well, I can assure you
sir it is not a pachyderm,
though it is definitely huge.
Not to worry, though.
You'll be vexed no more today--
Why aren't you stopping?
Did I or did I not give
you orders to desist?!
Hey, I told them to.
She's the one who kept on.
I sent you another one.
Did it go through?
How am I supposed to know?!
You had your phone
on you five days ago.
Stop mocking--
Oh, that's right;
your phone rang
like a bazillion times
while you were gone.
Even when we
weren't running tests.
She's was five feet
from me for half of these!
Who're you mad at?
Oh, just ignore him, hon.
He's running low on calcium.
I am not!
I realize you're preoccupied,
but if you think it's important,
I gleaned enough
data to work up
a rough sketch of
how D-Mail works.
What?!
I've calculated that one
second on the timer equals
an hour in reality,
moving upstream to the
flow of linear time...
That means a minute
thirty translates to five days.
Pretty balls-out
she locked on to
how to control the distance
a text travels back, huh?
Indeed. But being limited
to thirty-six characters
is still our Achilles' Heel.
I'd like to find a way
to improve on that,
if at all possible...
As it stands now,
it's not very practical.
Well, that's not such a big
deal if you don't have
to send anything really
large back in time...
Hey, maybe it's hard because of
the whole Car Black Hole thing.
I think you mean,
"Kerr" Black Hole.
That's it.
A Kerr Black Hole is too
tight to let big stuff through.
Maybe it just needs a
little, uh. practice...
Will you knock it off?!
I suggest rest.
We can hit the problem
with fresh minds tomorrow...
Each of us should
feel proud of what's
been accomplished here today.
Because of us,
August 2, 2010 is now a date
that will live in the
hearts of mankind forever!
On this day, the
Future Gadget Laboratory
breathed new life into a
dream as old as the hills...
For we have bridled time!
Well, except that SERN
kind of already beat us to it...
And saying we've bridled
it is presumptuous.
We're still stuck in
the preliminary phase.
I am attempting
to be poetic here...!
Must you insist on
sapping the thunder
out of every single utterance?!
Okarin...
I'm super proud of what
we've all accomplished here.
Where am I?
Don't panic.
You're not the one moving.
Time and space have
switched places here.
So this is an event horizon...
Space can no longer
be moved through,
and time as you understand
it ceases to exist.
One second to you,
for me stretches out past the
horizon line of what is real.
Are you saying that
space has fallen away?
That time has no part of it?
What's moving, then?
Me, or the universe?
Don't look back...
Eternity isn't infinite...
Reality has a
beginning and an end...
Always has. Always will.
If that's true...
Where does that leave me?
Move forward...
Look over the edge.
You're on my last nerve...
For cryin' out loud get a life.
"Sorry about yesterday."
"I really need to drop by
and talk to you soon."
Does it not occur to
you that people sleep?
Well who the Hell
wouldn't be at this hour?!
What?
Seriously? I'm right here.
Ugh. Whatever it
is, just say it...
Look, this is getting ridiculous
and it's very early...
Wait, is this your idea
of hounding yours truly
for an exclusive
interview or something?
Why won't you speak?
Oh, of course...
The aura of big, bad, legendary
mad scientist Hououin Kyouma
robs yet another innocent
lamb of her powers of speech!
It's just... easier...
sending texts...
I came here... to... uh... well,
you know... see the... IBN.
Very well... But see
is all you shall do...
That done, you will
leave at once. Understood?
Maybe she's just part
of what Daru calls
the "antiquing crowd."
Feel free, but beware...
Photograph my face
and you'll leave me no
choice but to silence--
You expect me to
let you borrow it?
And help you haul it?
What part of "look only" do you
fail to comprehend, my dear?
Besides, if you
intend to make off
with it you could at least do me
the kindness of asking out loud.
May I please... uh... borrow it?
I'm afraid you're
out of luck there...
I myself only have it
on loan for an interval
from a trusted friend...
I am honor-bound to return it
once my researches
are at an end.
So... who did you
borrow it from?
Some friends from
the Yanabayashi Shrine.
Good morrow, my peeps!
Oh... Hey I didn't
realize we had a guest.
Ah. You recall my
friend from yesterday...
This rotund fellow
is nothing less
than my right hand man,
our good hack, Daru.
Hacker, thank you very much.
Had a couple ideas
how we might tart up
the Phone Wave a
notch, by the way.
I mean it's such
an ass-pain as is.
Some serious tweakage
is needed if we're gonna
make sendin' mail to the past
user friendly, am I right?
Uh... Yes... You misheard him...
He, didn't say
"sending mail to the past,"
he said "Kending
eorfals du cree clast."
Ancient Sumerian, you see.
Yes, yes. Roughly translated,
it means "would you
care for an omelet?"
Good morning, Okarin...!
Mind if I heat up
my chicken tenders
before you start your
time travel experiments?
Morning everyone.
I think I had an "ah-ha" moment
about the time
machine last night.
It's me... Situation critical...
No, no... An outsider's
caught wind of numero eight...
Yes, of course I'll handle it.
Okay, what is it this time?
Apparently it involves
ignoring the three of us.
...the Organization know we're
performing experiments simi--
Damn it all, I'm trying
to have a conversation!
Is it true?
F... B?
Very well... I guess since
the cat's out of the bag...
I'm loath to do this, however...
Kiryuu Moeka...
As of this moment, I christen
you lab member Double-O Five!