¶
( chorus vocalizing )
Alice: I am Alice,
Integrity Knight
Alice Synthesis Thirty!
I am the proxy
of the three goddesses
who protect this realm!
I am the priestess of light,
and whoever dares defy me...
( Through skull )
Shall know the fury of my power!
( Gabriel gasps ) A-Alice.
( Chuckles )
Alicia.
This time...
This time,
her soul will be mine.
And once I have the lightcube
that holds her fluctlight
in my hands,
I'm going to savor
every last bite.
Subjects, your attention!
We are heading south,
Pugilists in the lead,
then Dark Knights,
then the Supply Corps.
That knight
is the priestess of light,
and she is
to be captured unharmed!
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( gear rattling )
Bercouli: The plan's working
a little too well.
Vecta's got his whole army
coming after you now.
He's obsessed with you.
No doubt about that.
Alice: We should
be thankful he is.
It is much better
than being ignored entirely.
Bercouli: All right,
let's talk about strategy.
I was thinking me and the troops
keep leading them south
and slowly chip away
at their ranks.
Seems like the best approach.
Alice: Agreed.
We have already wiped out
half of their numbers.
That leaves their main force,
the Dark Knights and Pugilists.
Chasing us will wear them down.
And if we can defeat
Emperor Vecta,
I have hope the remaining
people of this land
will be open to a truce.
Bercouli: Hmm.
That's a good hope to have.
Problem is,
who's gonna be in charge here
when Vecta's gone?
If only that punk shasta
was still alive.
Alice: Then, it is true.
The general
of the Dark Knights is dead?
Bercouli: Yeah.
I didn't see him
or his number two out there.
He would have been
our best shot to reason with.
- ( Wings flap )
- Hmm?
Huh?
Renly: I have finished
my reconnaissance, sir.
The shrubland south of here
should work for our ambush.
Bercouli: Thanks for
checking it out, kid.
Tell the units,
and get 'em ready to move out.
That dragon of yours
must be exhausted by now.
Make sure it gets food and water
before we go.
Renly: Sir!
¶
- ( wings flapping )
- ( Bercouli chuckles )
Alice: What is it?
Bercouli: Oh, nothin'.
I was just thinkin'.
Part of me's glad there won't
be any more synthesis rituals.
I mean, havin' your memory
and life stolen,
that's a horrible price to pay
to be a knight.
But then, part of me's also
kinda sad we won't be seeing
any more young'uns like Renly
joining the order.
Alice: Perhaps we won't.
However, stolen memories
and lives do not make a knight.
I know of no such rule, uncle.
Do you?
When we are all gone, our souls,
our will, our purpose,
they remain to inspire
those we leave behind.
That is what I believe.
- ( Explosion )
- ( Gasps )
( Dark Knights and
Pugilists yelling )
¶
Alice: Here they come.
( Iskahn yelling )
Bercouli: Damn Pugilists.
They'll be a handful for us.
If you hit 'em
with your bare fist,
they'll happily take it.
But if you come at 'em
with a sword,
they refuse to get cut.
Alice: What? "Refuse"?
Bercouli: Yup,
that's what I said.
See, the more training
they go through,
the more they think a sword's
nothing to be scared of,
so watch out when you fight 'em,
'cause they can
will their skin to get hard,
and they can deflect any blade.
We'll have to keep 'em busy
'til the others are
in position for the ambush.
( Alice grunts )
Sheyta: I shall
go and face them.
( Both gasping )
¶
( Iskahn grunts )
I can't wait to fight
one of them
super strong integrity knights.
Eh? ( Grunts )
Who are you supposed to be,
and why are you in the way?
¶
Sheyta: Hmm.
I am a knight.
I am here to keep you
from advancing further.
( Iskahn laughs )
By the looks of you,
you couldn't stop a kid
from getting by!
Wait. Let me guess.
All you can do
is cast arts, right?
Sheyta: Mm.
I am not skilled
in formal arts.
( Iskahn grunts )
Ah, whatever.
Go kick her ass, Yotte.
Yotte: You got it!
( Chuckles )
Sheyta: Just you, then?
Yotte: I'm way more than you
can handle, you beanpole!
Now shut up,
and draw your sword.
- ( Iskahn gasps )
- ( Pugilists murmuring )
Iskahn: Damn, that's skinny.
( Yotte growls )
I'll break you in half!
- ( Clang )
- ( Iskahn chuckles )
( Yotte gasps )
( Wailing )
- ( Sobbing )
- ( Sheyta sighs )
¶
Administrator: I've heard that
you prefer keeping to yourself.
Why is that, I wonder.
Do people scare you?
Or perhaps...
Your urge to slice them
scares you.
( Sheyta grunts )
( Gasps )
Administrator: I knew it.
I can see in your eyes
that it does.
If you had your way, you'd
slice up everything in sight.
You feel like you're cursed
with a drive for murder.
Cheer up. There's no reason
to feel ashamed about it.
In fact, I can help you
use it to your advantage.
( Sheyta grunts )
Administrator: On your last
reconnaissance mission
into the dark territory,
you brought
this flower back to me.
It absorbed massive amounts
of the spatial resources
generated on the battlefield.
I will turn it
into your divine object,
a sword with
the highest priority level
that can cut through anything.
( Sheyta gasps )
With this sword, you shall wield
a manifestation of the curse
carved into your soul.
Take it, and serve me
with your murderous impulse.
The curse you were born with
now has a purpose.
Slice and hack and slash away,
and at the end
of your blood-smeared path,
you will find the key
to breaking your curse.
At least, you might.
( Yotte wailing )
( Pugilists gasping )
¶
( Iskahn gasps )
( Pugilists screaming )
Alice: What a savage
fighting style.
And yet, as violent
as her attacks are,
I do not detect any hostility
or any emotion, for that matter.
Bercouli: I've known her
for more than a hundred years,
and I still have no idea
what goes on in her head,
not even a clue.
Don't worry about her.
She can handle 'em.
But we should go before
the main force catches up.
Come on. We have to make sure
everyone's ready
and waiting for 'em.
Alice: Right.
¶
Soldier: All the units
are in position.
( Renly grunts )
According to Commander Bercouli,
the Pugilists
are vulnerable to sacred arts.
The plains might not have
enough spatial resources,
but here, there's
at least some vegetation,
so the priests should have
enough sacred power
to launch an attack.
Hopefully it'll cause confusion,
and we can use our dragons
to burn them.
( Gasps )
Are the Supply Corps
somewhere safe?
Soldier: Yes.
They're standing by
to the south.
They're far enough back
that they won't get caught
in the battle.
Renly: Very good. Thank you.
Guard: Hmm?
( Grunts )
( Gagging )
¶
( Vassago chuckles )
Come on, man.
I'm getting bored
sitting around, giving orders.
How's about we go outside
and have ourselves some fun?
Gabriel: No, thanks.
But you can go first
if you want to.
I'll pick a spot.
There. In those woods.
Vassago: That better be
where the action is,
or I'm gonna be disappointed!
Gabriel: I guarantee
you'll have fun,
pk-ing, that is.
¶
Vassago: Five down, baby.
( Sword slicing )
( Pugilists yelling )
( Iskahn growls )
How dare you?
You're gonna pay for this!
To these fists of mine,
your armor's nothin' but paper!
( Sheyta grunts )
( Iskahn grunts )
¶
( growls )
( Yells )
( Clang )
( Grunts )
Well, well, well.
You might look like a girl,
but you're as hard as a rock.
Sheyta: I am not a girl.
I am older than you.
Iskahn: Huh?
Yeah, I know you are.
You're an Integrity Knight.
You're all supposed to be
immortal freaks or whatever.
So what, do you want me
to call you granny instead?
( Sheyta grunts )
I'll allow it.
However, you are also freakish.
Your skin is so hard,
I could barely cut into it.
( Iskahn scoffs )
Deal with it, granny.
Besides, folks like us need
an edge against you knights,
what with
your demon powers and all.
You charged in
and chopped up all my people.
( Pugilists moaning )
( Iskahn gasps )
You maimed 'em.
You were holding back,
weren't you?
What do you think we are,
training dummies?
You takin' pity on us? Huh?!
I'm gonna beat you
to death personally.
( Pugilists chanting )
( Chanting stops )
( Iskahn shudders )
Here I come, woman!
( Sheyta gasps )
Iskahn: What did you expect,
that all us Pugilists did
was punch?!
( Grunts )
See ya!
( Gasps )
( Growls )
¶
( Sheyta coughs )
Iskahn: Now that
your armor's gone,
you're lookin'
way more like a fighter,
although you don't got
nearly enough muscles.
You should eat
and train more, woman.
Sheyta: As should you.
Just now,
you became a bit softer.
Iskahn: Eh?
Aw, who you callin' soft?!
I was just getting warmed up!
Now that I am, you're
gonna see me at full power,
so don't hold back!
Give me all you got!
And wipe that sleepy look
off your face already!
Sheyta: Eh?
( Sighing )
I trust that will suffice.
Come, then.
Iskahn: Eh?
All right, you asked for it.
( Breathing deeply )
¶
( Sheyta sighs )
( Iskahn gasps )
I'm so fired up for this.
I never fought
anyone like her before!
( Growls )
( Pugilists yell )
Sheyta: Strange,
how I allow
this battle to continue.
It must be this one's attack.
He seems weak
everywhere except his fists,
but he displays a will
worthy of an Integrity Knight.
I could end this
by cutting off his head.
I should, but...
I wonder if I can slice
through that fist?
This is fun.
( Iskahn grunts, chuckles )
Even though she looks
like some weak upper-class lady
from the human empire,
deep down, she's the same as me.
Uh-oh. She's gonna overpower me.
Oh, well.
If I'm gonna die,
this ain't a bad way to go.
- ( Pugilist grunts )
- ( Iskahn grunts )
What in the hell'd
you do that for, Dampa!
Dampa: We're out of time,
champion.
Main force is almost here.
( Iskahn growls )
Hey, woman! Don't you
go thinkin' you won this fight!
Sheyta: Look here.
I do have a name,
- not "Woman."
- Iskahn: Whatever.
The main force is almost here,
and we got you surrounded, so--
- ( wings flap )
- ( Pugilists gasp )
¶
Iskahn: Lousy dragons.
Go on, and go,
but at least tell me your name
before you run away!
Sheyta: I am not running away.
And for your information,
my name is
Sheyta Synthesis Twelve.
( Iskahn growls )
¶
( Vassago chuckles )
That's it. A little closer.
( Gasps )
( Ronie grunts )
Vassago: 'Sup, baby doll?
How'd you spot me?
Ronie: It wasn't too hard.
My mentor taught me to trust
my senses, not my eyes.
Vassago: What?
Where have I heard that?
( Ronie inhales )
Wake up! The enemy's here!
( Vassago scoffs )
( Growls )
¶
( chuckles )
Oh, boys, time to party!
( Footsteps thumping )
¶
( soldiers gasping )
Renly: What?!
The enemy's behind us?
Dozens of them?
If they destroy our supplies,
we will be immobilized.
And those two girls and kirito
are back there.
I should send backup,
but if I do,
the enemy will know
about our ambush.
Or could they already know?
Maybe I should send all
of these troops back to help.
Bercouli: I guess they figured
we'd head this way
after we broke through,
so they stuck some troops
down here to meet us.
Renly: C-Commander!
Bercouli: Hmm. Renly...
Get the troops
up and out of here.
Kiddo, go and help
the Supply Corps.
I'll stay here and hold off
the Pugilists. Understood?
Renly: Sir!
Alice: You say
you'll hold them off,
but how?
They are 5,000. You are but one.
Bercouli: Kid, don't worry.
I got this. Now get goin'.
Alice: All right, then.
Please be safe.
Bercouli: Hmph.
( Vassago laughs )
( Ronie yelping )
- Tiese: Ronie!
- ( Soldiers gasp )
( Vassago laughs )
( Tiese gasps )
Vassago: There it is,
that old feeling.
God damn,
I missed the rush of it,
a life hanging
by the edge of my sword.
This right here's why I can't
get enough of player killing.
( Ronie whimpers )
Huh?
Vassago: Eh?
( Energy crackling )
Ronie: Is that lady stacia?
( Gasps )
( Woman vocalizing )
Dark Knight:
Th-the ground's opening up!
( Dark Knights screaming )
( Vocalizing continues )
Vassago: Holy crap.
You gotta be kidding me.
Same hair, same face. It's her!
The Killer Queen of
the Knights of the Blood Oath,
Lightning Flash.
( Singing in Japanese )
¶