¶
- ( Clatter )
- ( Alice gasps )
( Kirito gasping )
( Approaching footsteps )
( Alice gasps )
Kirito...
You cannot fight, but I can.
Do not worry.
I shall rescue them
and come right back.
I promise.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Alice: Goblins.
( Goblins growling, laughing )
Goblin: Kill 'em! Kill 'em all!
( Men gasp )
Alice: Why don't they
flee south, where it is clear?
Alice: Amayori, wait here.
Gasfut: Should the enemy
breach our defenses,
you must hold them back!
Barbossa: You hear that?!
Stand your ground,
and keep those things
out of our village!
( Villagers gasp, yell )
- Gasfut: Eh?
- Man: What is it?
( Villagers gasping, murmuring )
¶
Selka: Alice?
( Alice grunts )
Look...
They will surround you
if you stay here.
Have everyone evacuate
by the south road
while you still have time.
Barbossa: A-are you insane?!
My mansion--i mean,
this village is our home!
Alice: It can be rebuilt,
but, if you stay,
you will surely be slaughtered.
Which is more important,
your possessions or your lives?
( Barbossa sputters, sighs )
Gasfut: We must stay,
because it is what zink,
our man-at-arms, ordered.
We are
the last line of defense.
In this situation,
everyone must do what he says,
even I, the village elder.
( Alice gasps )
Gasfut: Imperial law
is clear on that.
Selka: We should do
as my sister says.
( Gasfut gasps )
Selka: Please, father.
( Alice sighs )
Selka.
( Selka grunts )
Listen to her.
You know she speaks the truth.
Our lives are more important!
I know we have to follow
the laws of the land,
but, even so...
If we stay, we die!
Barbossa: We can't
abandon our homes!
You're just a child,
and you should mind your tongue!
We will stay
and protect the village!
( Gasps )
¶
I-I see now.
This is your doing, isn't it?!
These things
from the dark territory
wouldn't be here
if not for you, Alice!
Years ago, when you were a child
and trespassed onto their land,
you were tainted!
You're a witch!
She is in league
with the monsters!
Alice: I am a knight,
and I revoke
the man-at-arms's order.
You will all
evacuate the village
by the south road at once!
Those of you bearing weapons
shall take the lead.
Barbossa: You--
you cannot be a knight,
not in this village.
There's no calling
for them here!
You can handle a sword
reasonably well,
but claiming to be a knight
is outrageous!
What if a knight from centoria
heard this?!
Alice: My name is Alice.
¶
I am one of the three knights
who oversee centoria,
an integrity knight
of the church,
Alice Synthesis Thirty!
- ( Villagers murmuring )
- ( Barbossa gasps )
Y-You're an integrity knight?!
Selka: Why didn't you tell me?
Alice: In truth,
I was afraid to.
The knighthood
is both my duty...
And my punishment.
Selka: I knew
you weren't a sinner.
Deep down, I knew!
I always believed in you!
( Thump )
Gasfut: I will do
as the lady knight commands.
We shall evacuate.
( Alice gasps )
Gasfut: All those
bearing weapons
will lead the villagers
to the south gate at once!
As soon as everyone is out,
evacuate to the forest
south of the clearing!
( Villagers chattering )
Man: I need help with
the wounded and the elderly!
Man 2: Right behind you!
Hey, you over there, follow us!
Alice: Keep them safe, father--
Selka and mother, everyone.
Gasfut: Yes, milady.
Be safe as well.
Selka: Be careful.
Don't get yourself hurt.
Alice: Amayori!
( Amayori roars )
( Goblins chattering, laughing )
( Zink gasps )
There's way too many.
Fall back! Retreat!
- ( Gasps )
- Alice: Burn them!
Goblin: Eh?
( Goblins scream )
( Chorus vocalizing )
¶
Barbossa: It'll burn everything!
Selka: Alice has a dragon?
Zink: Whoa.
( Gasps )
( Goblins yell )
Zink: What are you doing here?
Alice: There is
no time to explain.
Follow the others to safety.
Hurry up!
Goblin: I'll kill ye
and eat yer guts, ium woman!
¶
( Goblins yelling )
( Orc growls )
Alice: From this moment on,
I fight for that
which is important to me,
the lives of my sister
and parents.
I fight...
For the sake of what Kirito and
eugeo sacrificed everything for,
the people.
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Goblins and Orcs yelling )
Alice: Thank you, Kirito.
I am all right now.
Though I may still falter,
my purpose is crystal clear.
I shall persevere
for the sake of our cause.
Halt! My name is Alice.
As long as I live,
the human realm
will not fall to you, so begone!
Return to your homeland now,
or you will die where you stand!
Enhance armament!
Orc: Forward!
You stupid ium girl!
I'm morikka the foot harvester,
and your bone--
( gasping )
Alice: Storm and churn...
My flowers!
( Morikka whimpers )
( Goblins and Orcs yelling )
( Alice sighs ) Hear me!
The end mountains
separate our lands.
Dig through it if you will,
but, as long
as we knights exist,
you are not
to set foot here again.
Make your choice!
Step forward,
and drown in your blood,
or retreat
to your land of darkness!
( Raiders yelling )
Selka: Mm?
( Gasps )
( Villagers cheering )
( Amayori roars )
( Overlapping chatter )
( Hammering )
Girl: Don't cry.
I'll make you a new doll.
Girl 2: Thanks.
Selka: Father wanted
to come see you off,
but, with the repairs...
Alice: No, I understand.
One day, when I
have fulfilled my duties,
I will return,
not as a knight,
but as Alice Zuberg.
Perhaps then
I shall be able to say...
"I have come home, father."
¶
( thinking ) I will return
to this village someday.
And, even if I fall in battle,
I know my heart will.
¶
( Man chuckles )
( Energy surges )
Man 2: Where the hell
is everyone?
Man 3: Hiding. Duh!
Man 1: Locate them.
Man 3: There you go.
The sub control room.
Higa: I patched in
to the backup power.
The subcon's up and running
and ready for action now!
( Kikuoka grunts )
Asuna: You better pray
Kirito wakes up again,
because, if he doesn't,
I swear I'll make you pay!
( Sandal taps )
( Kikuoka gasps )
( Sighs )
I know. I know.
I'm going to do everything I can
to bring him back. I promise.
- ( Gasping )
- ( Sandals clatter )
Rinko: Take it easy.
You will get him back,
but this isn't the way to do it.
Try to stay calm.
Asuna: You're right.
I'm okay now.
Just overreacted there
for a minute.
( Door hisses )
Kikuoka: Huh?
Nakanishi: Reporting in.
The primary
and secondary bulkheads
are sealed and secure.
Also, all noncombat personnel
have been evacuated
to the bow block.
Kikuoka: Good work.
About how long
will the bulkheads hold?
Nakanishi: Depends.
If they have saws, eight hours.
A few minutes
if they have explosives,
but they won't go with that,
not on the primary bulkhead.
Kikuoka: It's too close
to the lightcube cluster.
All right,
let's see where we stand.
Casualties first.
Please tell me everyone's okay.
Nakanishi: They are, sir.
Three civvies
with the research team
sustained minor injuries.
As for our S.D.F. Unit,
it suffered two minor
and two heavy injuries.
It's nothing life-threatening.
They're being treated now.
Kikuoka: What about the ship?
Nakanishi: Not so good, sir.
The bulkheads from
the bilge dock to main control
are offline
and can't be accessed remotely.
But the real issue is power.
The main line was cut,
so we're on auxiliary now.
The good news
is we have stable power
all through the ship.
The bad news is
we can't rotate the screw props
without rebooting
the whole system.
Kikuoka: Like a sea turtle
without fins
and with a shark
nipping at its belly.
Nakanishi: Yes.
They got the bilge dock
and all 12 sectors
in the lower shaft.
( Sighs ) The bastards.
They got us good.
Nakanishi: They did.
All right,
they have main control,
S.T.L. One,
and the nuclear reactor.
They don't want to destroy us.
If they did,
they would've blown us
out of the water by now.
The next question is...
Who the hell are these people?
Higa, what do you think?
Higa: Oh. Um...
Let's have a looksie.
( Both gasp )
Higa: Going by their suits
and the hardware
they're packing,
I'd say they were mercs.
And, based on
their average size,
I'm pretty sure
they're not Asian.
Kikuoka: Well,
look on the bright side.
At least
we're not being attacked
by our own special forces,
which is a relief.
We can also be sure
of one other thing.
Whoever these people are,
they know about
project alicization.
Higa: Yup, you got that right.
They broke in
through the bilge deck
and headed straight
for the main control room.
They know about the S.T.L.,
and they know
we have a true bottom-up A.I.
They're here for Alice.
( Both gasp )
Higa: Fortunately,
I locked main con down in time.
( Chuckles ) I fixed it
so they can't interfere
with the simulation
or eject Alice's fluctlight
from the lightcube cluster.
Kikuoka: That's fantastic,
but, then, neither can we.
Higa: No, we can't.
No one can eject
Alice's lightcube externally,
either them in main
or us in here.
But that's a good thing!
I mean, it's pretty much
a win for our side.
They can't access the cluster
by computer,
and they won't
break through the wall,
'cause they know
they'll damage it.
It's only a matter of time
'til the "Asahi"
comes with backup.
Then it's game over
for those dumb-asses.
Game over!
Kikuoka: But we still don't know
if we're playing the game
or getting played.
- Higa: Huh?
- Kikuoka: We're here.
Where's the "Asahi"?
Nakanishi: Waiting, sir.
¶
the fleet command
in Yokosuka ordered her
to keep her distance and
stand by until further notice.
They seem to think
we've been taken hostage
and are sitting tight
until the attackers
make their demands.
Kikuoka: Here's what I think.
Our guests
have to have a back channel
to someone high up in the S.D.F.
And, if I'm right,
the "Asahi" won't move in
until Alice's lightcube
has been retrieved.
Higa: Well, now we know.
We're not dealing
with terrorists here.
This isn't good.
If these guys are
what I think they are,
they'll have
an expert with 'em!
Kikuoka: Who might realize
they can eject the cube
from inside the underworld.
Since they have
control of S.T.L. One,
they can drop someone in
and use the virtual console
to execute the command.
Rinko: And if they do that,
then what?
Kikuoka: The target cube
will be extracted
from the lightcube cluster
in the center of the main shaft.
Then, it'll be sent
through an air tube
to a hatch
in the selected control room.
The hatch
for this room's over there.
The other's in main con,
with them.
( Typing )
Well, now that we
know what they want,
we have to retrieve Alice's
fluctlight before they do.
Right now, that's up to Kirito.
Once again...
All our hopes
are riding on his shoulders.
Higa, how is he?
What's his status currently?
Higa: Well,
the short version is...
He's stable now,
but he's on the edge
of not good.
( Asuna gasping )
Higa:
That death gun dude's toxin
damaged Kirito's neural network.
And that's not something
conventional treatment can help.
We thought the S.T.L.
Could stimulate
the growth of a new network,
so we blocked his memory and
dropped him into the underworld.
But, this time,
his memory didn't get blocked,
probably 'cause of
the neural damage.
He woke up in there
as his real-world self,
and we didn't find out
until he called us.
Rinko: What? Hang on a second.
What about time?
It's accelerated
in the underworld.
How much time has passed
in there since he dove in?
Higa: About 2 1/2 years.
For that whole time,
he's been interacting
with the artificial fluctlights
like they were real people.
He also knew that,
once the simulation ended,
his new friends
and their world would be erased.
That's why
he went to the console
in the central cathedral,
since that was the only way
to get ahold of us.
Or rather keeks here.
I bet he was gonna
try to convince you
to spare them and their world.
He had to fight like hell
to get to that console,
but he made it,
thanks to some friends.
I couldn't check the event log
during all the commotion here,
but his friends helped him
in the fight
with the axiom church.
Some didn't make it.
When he got through to us,
he was in mental distress,
blaming himself
for the death of his friends.
And, by doing that, he ended up
attacking his own fluctlight.
It was right about then
when those jackasses
cut the power line.
That caused a short circuit,
and the surge from that caused
a spike in the S.T.L.'s output.
As a result,
Kirito's self-destructive
impulse was actualized.
Then his ego was deactivated.
Rinko: I don't get it.
His ego was deactivated?
I didn't know that was possible.
Higa: Have a look at the screen.
That's a fluctlight,
Kirito's fluctlight
to be precise.
And that black hole
right there...
Is where a person's self-image
should be.
Rinko: The self-image,
the idea, concept,
or mental image of oneself.
Higa: Yup.
All of your decision making
passes through a simple yes-no
pathway in your fluctlight.
It asks whether you should
or shouldn't do something
based on
whatever situation you're in.
For example, Dr. Kojiro,
when you're
at your fave beef-bowl place,
you ever order a second helping?
Rinko: Mm, no.
Higa: Even if in your mind,
you're like,
"Damn, this is good.
I could eat another bowl"?
Rinko: Never.
Higa: And that's
your self-image pathway at work.
Decisions
can't lead to actions
unless they go
through those circuits.
In Kirito's case, his fluctlight
is damaged in that one spot.
He can't process
what happens around him,
and he can't initiate an action.
All he can do, I think, is stuff
he remembers from repetition--
eating, sleeping,
stuff like that.
Right now, I don't think
he knows who he is
or what he should do,
and he can't speak,
so he can't ask for help.
But that's just my theory.
( Asuna sighs )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Typing )
( Man chuckles )
( Whistles )
( Man 2 chuckles )