( Army yelling )
¶
( Shibori growls )
( Roars )
¶
( Iskahn chuckles )
( Renly shudders )
( Soldiers gasp )
( Energy crackling )
Vassago: Nice.
This final load test's dope.
Yo, are you seein' all this?
It's better than a movie.
I'm starting to think we should
snag this graphics tech
instead of the A.I.,
go to Hollywood,
start an effects studio.
Dude, we'd be raking in money
faster than we could spend it.
Gabriel: I hate
to break it to you,
but all the stuff you're seeing
can't be saved to media.
Things in this world aren't
made up of polygon models.
The only way
to experience this show
is by being connected
to the s.T.L.
Soldiers of the Dark Empire,
at long last,
our time has come!
Ravage the humans
and their land!
Kill everything
that stands in your way!
Show no mercy!
( Soldiers yelling )
Gabriel: First battalion,
begin your assault!
( Goblins yelling )
Shibori: Kill 'em! Kill 'em all!
( Giants groaning )
Sigurosig: Crush them!
( Goblins yelling )
Kosogi: Forward!
¶
Fanatio: First unit, ready!
Draw your swords!
Priests, prepare
your healing incantations!
Priests: System call.
Generate luminous element.
Deusolbert: Come, then.
Eldrie: These vile creatures.
We will show them
what we're made of.
( Soldiers yelling )
( Renly gasps )
¶
Alice: It has begun.
I shall do...
What I must.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Goblins yelling )
¶
Woman: Wake up, my dear.
It's morning.
Deusolbert: It is the one memory
I have left of my past.
I cannot even recall
when it was or who.
Though you are long gone,
I will protect
the world we shared.
This, I swear.
Enhance armament!
¶
I am Deusolbert
synthesis seven!
Whosoever stands before me
shall be burned to ashes!
( Goblins yell )
( Screaming )
( Deusolbert grunts )
( Goblins scream )
Bercouli: First, we'll restore
the order
of the integrity knights.
Then we'll muster the imperial
knights of the four empires
and train them for battle.
There's strength in numbers,
and right now,
we need all the help we can get.
I know what I told you
is hard to accept,
but it's still our job
to protect the people here.
I can't do that without you.
Fanatio: Commander...
I shall follow you
wherever you go.
Found him.
Enhance armament!
Pierce him! Divine light!
Sigurosig: Eh?
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Giant groans )
( Sigurosig gasping )
Fizel: Ooh!
The fighting's started!
Linel: Yup, yup!
Fizel:
Uncle Deusolbert's already
killed a bunch with his arrows.
Linel: The vice commander's
killed bunches, too.
- Fizel: What's with them?
- Linel: Yeah,
the left flank seems
a bit weak, doesn't it?
Fizel: Mm-hmm. Sure,
Eldrie has amazing skills,
but as a knight, he's never been
in a battle like this before.
Linel: And then there's
renlicchi behind him,
not the most reliable.
Fizel: Poor thing.
He'd be better off
all the way in back
with the supply corps.
Linel: Speaking of,
I heard that kirito boy's
sitting back there.
( Both giggle )
- ( Goblins growling )
- Kosogi: Stay together!
Follow my lead,
and don't stop for anything!
¶
Eldrie: Do not
let a single one past us!
Cut them all down!
Soldiers: Yes, sir!
( Kosogi growling )
Eldrie: What is that?
Kosogi: Throw 'em! Now!
Soldier: Huh?
- ( Soldiers yelp )
- Eldrie: What in blazes...
Kosogi: Get down! Keep running!
( Goblins growling )
Soldier 2: Get back here,
you filthy--
Eldrie: No! You'll strike down
one of ours in all this smoke!
They're headed
for the rear unit.
I pray sir Renly
can hold them at bay.
Soldier 2: The left flank
has been breached by Goblins!
They are on their way!
Where is sir Renly?
( Soldiers mutter )
Soldier 3: We don't know.
He was here when all
the fighting started.
( Renly panting )
¶
( Deusolbert grunts )
( Goblins screaming )
Shibori: That one!
That Archer there!
Surround him,
and stomp his bones!
( Goblins yelling )
Golgorosso:
Protect sir Deusolbert!
Don't let
any of the wretches through!
Deusolbert: Thank you.
I'll hurry.
Golgorosso: We won't fail you.
( Soldiers yelling )
( Deusolbert grunts )
( Goblins screaming )
( Giants gasping )
Sigurosig:
How could a human do this?
I've never felt
such fear before.
It can't be.
- ( Static crackling )
- It can't be.
It can't be. It can't be.
It can't be.
Kill. Kill. Kill.
Kill. Kill. Kill. Kil--
kill! Ki-ki-kill!
Kill!
( Yells )
( Giants groaning )
( Sigurosig screams )
Kill! Kill! Kill!
( Fanatio gasps )
I can't move.
( Gasps )
Sigurosig: Kill! Kill! Kill!
Fanatio: Why?
Sigurosig: Kill the human! Kill!
Kill! Kill!
( Fanatio grunts )
Sigurosig: Ki-l!
Fanatio: Commander.
Woman: Lady Fanatio!
Fanatio: Dakira?!
( Dakira grunting )
¶
( Screams )
( Sigurosig grunts )
Fanatio: Dakira!
( Gasps )
( Dakira gasping )
Fanatio: Dakira!
Don't die!
Stay still.
I shall tend to your wounds.
Dakira: Lady Fanatio...
I've always...
Adored you...
And shall...
Forever.
( Sighs )
¶
Whirling Blades: We shall
protect you, lady Fanatio!
Fanatio: I shall avenge you.
I swear!
- ( Chorus vocalizing )
- ( Sigurosig roars )
( Whirling Blades gasp )
( Static crackling )
K-Kill!
Kill!
¶
( Gasping )
Kill the human!
Fanatio: Your grave awaits you.
( Giants gasping )
First unit, center, advance!
Push the enemy back!
( Soldiers yelling )
( Metal clashing )
( Goblins scream )
Deusolbert: So this
is what war is like.
I cannot even tell
how long we've been fighting.
( Goblins scream )
( Deusolbert panting )
This is madness.
They keep rushing
to their deaths.
Hmm?
( Sighs )
Shibori: Look what we got here,
an Archer with no more arrows.
¶
Deusolbert: You are a Chief
of the Goblin Tribe, I take it,
one of the Council of Ten?
Shibori: That's right,
Chief of the Flatland Goblins,
Lord Shibori!
Deusolbert:
I am an integrity knight,
Deusolbert Synthesis Seven--
Shibori: So what?! I don't care
what your name is, Ium!
You're just meat to me,
and once I chop off your head,
you'll make a fine meal!
Enough talk!
Rush him, and hold him!
( Goblins yelling )
Deusolbert: How absurd!
- ( Grunts )
- ( Goblin groans )
( Goblin yells )
( Gags )
Deusolbert: That leaves four.
( Goblins chuckle )
( Shibori growls )
( Deusolbert gasps )
( Shibori roars )
Golgorosso: Die, monster!
Shibori: Eh?
( Golgorosso yells )
( Groaning )
( Shibori chuckles )
¶
( Deusolbert growls )
( Roars )
¶
Come, o flames!
( Goblins whimpering )
( Goblin screams )
Shibori: Eh?
Eh?
Deusolbert: Burn to ashes!
( Shibori grunts )
( Goblins gasping )
( Screaming )
( Flames roar )
( Goblins scream )
¶
- Soldier: Commander.
- Bercouli: Hmm?
Soldier: Lady Fanatio
killed the Giant's Chief.
Sir Deusolbert
killed a Goblin Chief.
They're holding the line now.
Bercouli: Mm. What else?
Soldier: Well, my lord,
as you can see,
the enemy forces outnumber us.
We're holding them off,
but it's only a matter of time
before they punch through.
Bercouli: Got any word
about their airborne support?
Soldier: So far, they're
not using dragons or minions,
just ground troops.
Bercouli: Hmm.
( Screams and yells echoing )
¶
( Alice gasps )
( Amayori trills )
Alice: I will be fine.
¶
( chorus vocalizing )
( Distant yells echoing )
¶
( Renly sobbing )
( Singing in Japanese )
¶