( Heart beating )
( Chorus vocalizing )
Man: Gabriel.
¶
- Gabriel.
- Hmm?
Man: Did you know that bugs
don't have brains like we do?
Gabriel: Then what kind
of brains do they have?
Man: Their nervous system
acts as their brain,
and it runs
all throughout their bodies.
That's why,
if you remove their head,
an insect can continue living
for a bit.
Gabriel: If this can stay alive
after its head is gone,
then I wonder
where its soul's at?
( Exoskeleton cracks )
Girl: Yoo-hoo!
Gabriel: Eh?
( Girl laughs ) Hi, Gabe!
¶
( laughs )
Gabriel: Hi, Alicia.
Alicia: I'm bored.
Wanna hang out?
Gabriel: Okay!
( Alicia humming )
Gabriel: I wonder
where Alicia's soul is?
¶
people aren't like bugs,
can't live without our heads,
so a person's soul
has to be in their head.
It's gotta be
somewhere in the brain.
Under her skin, her skull,
deep in her brain,
her soul's there, hiding.
( Gabriel sighs )
( Gasps )
¶
( gauntlet creaks )
Hmph.
Vassago: No way.
Is that you?
Gabriel: Vassago?
Vassago: Oh, yeah. You know it.
Check it out.
That dork logged us in
and didn't screw it up.
Gabriel: Mm-hmm.
( Thinking ) A world
of artificial fluctlights,
and every one of them
with a soul, a human soul.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Goblins yelling, laughing )
Kubiri: Run, you bastards!
Us flatland goblins
should be the ones
to get to the emperor first!
( Yelling continues )
Hagashi: Those flatland
slug slurpers won't beat us!
The honor
of his majesty's first spear
will go to the mountain goblins!
¶
( Ogres growling )
Iskahn: Let's get to the palace
before the other tribes!
Pugilists: Yeah!
Iskahn: Move out!
( Fu Za chuckles )
¶
Rengil: I am the head
of the commerce guild,
your excellency.
Rengil gila scobo
at your service.
Lilpilin: I be Lilpilin,
chief of orcs!
Dee: I am Dee eye ell,
your majesty,
head of the dark mages guild.
It is my privilege to serve you.
My 3,000 mages, my heart,
and my body belong to you.
Gabriel: Hmm.
Shasta: Vixur ul Shasta,
head of the dark knights.
Before I pledge my sword,
I have a question.
Your majesty, now that
you've returned after so long,
what do you seek?
Gabriel: Blood and terror,
fire and destruction,
death and screams.
( Council members gasp )
Gabriel: The western lands flow
with the power of the gods that
banished me from the heavens,
but the great gate
that protects those lands
shall crumble very soon,
and so I've returned.
This world shall know my power
and tremble before it.
Once the great gate falls,
the realm of the humans
will belong
to the people of darkness.
I have but one request of you,
to bring me
the priestess of light
who resides in the human empire.
You have permission to terrorize
and murder any other human,
but she is mine.
Go forth,
my warriors of darkness!
Claim your destiny!
Lilpilin: Kill!
Drink their blood!
Smash in their skulls,
and rip 'em to pieces!
( Hagashi roars )
Hail to the emperor!
Kubiri: War!
Death to the white iums!
( Subjects cheering )
¶
Vassago: I gotta
hand it to you, bro.
You got some talent.
You could be a big-time actor
if you wanted.
Gabriel: Please,
don't be ridiculous.
A speech was called for,
and I gave it,
which is a skill
you should learn yourself.
Since you are their superior,
they'll be expecting it.
Vassago: I don't wanna
give orders or speeches.
I just wanna kill some fools.
I never seen v.R. Be so real,
so I figure I might as well
take advantage of it.
I mean, I can
friggin' taste this wine!
Gabriel: Just remember,
there's no pain absorber here.
If you get cut,
it'll bleed and hurt, bad.
Vassago: I know.
That's what makes this great!
¶
- Critter: That you, captain?
- Gabriel: Yeah.
Critter: Good timing.
We got back
to main control just now,
wanted to make sure
your dive didn't have issues.
Gabriel: Thank you.
So far,
our first day here went well.
The phenomenon
of accelerated time
takes a bit of getting used to.
Other than that,
everything's going as planned,
so I'm not complaining.
We should have these units
equipped and ready
in two days, our time.
Then we'll launch the attack
on the human empire.
Critter: Suh-weet.
All right, so here's what to do.
Once you have Alice,
get her back to that terminal,
and bring up the menu.
There'll be an option there
to eject her lightcube
to the main control room.
Click on that, and Alice's
lightcube's as good as ours.
Oh, and while you're there,
there's something
you and that dumb-ass Vassago
- should keep in mind.
- Vassago: What?!
Critter: Since we don't have
access to admin privileges,
we don't have
the luxury of resetting,
so if you gents end up
getting killed, I won't be able
to log you back in
with those superuser accounts.
The best I can do is send
you back as low-level grunts.
Gabriel: Got it.
We'll be careful.
What's the s.D.F. Up to?
Critter: Nothing at the moment.
I bet they're so freaked out,
they don't even know
you dove in there.
Gabriel: Good.
I guess that's it for now.
Hopefully, the next time you
hear from me, we'll have Alice.
Critter: Roger that! Good luck.
Vassago: God,
I hate that ass-wipe.
I was thinking.
Maybe I'll head downtown
and, you know,
blow off a little steam.
Gabriel: No, I'd prefer it
if you didn't.
Once the op's over, you can
have a night all to yourself.
Vassago: All right.
Standing down
on the chicks and murder.
I'll hit the sack
and dream about 'em instead.
( Gabriel grunts )
What are you doing here?
Lipia: I shall be
your company tonight,
if it pleases your majesty.
Gabriel: Well.
( Bed creaks )
And by whose order?
Lipia: No one.
My duty is to indulge
your whims, sire.
Gabriel: All right, then.
Lipia: If you please...
( Blade scrapes )
( Grunting )
( Gags )
Gabriel: Who put you up to this?
Lipia: I am here
of my own volition.
Gabriel: Then who's
your commanding officer?
- Lipia: No one.
- Gabriel: Still,
you must have a reason
for your treachery.
Did you do it for money, or did
someone promise you status?
Lipia: For the good of the land.
( Gabriel chuckles ) Really?
Lipia: If war breaks out,
it will set history back
hundreds of years.
We cannot revert
to the old ways,
where the powerless
suffered under oppression.
( Gagging )
¶
( Crack )
( Gabriel gasps )
( Soft hum )
There it is,
just like that day.
¶
( Gabriel shuddering )
( Handle clatters )
( Gasps )
( Soft hum )
I just saw Alicia's soul,
and for a second there,
I could see
what her soul was seeing, too.
( Sighs )
A human soul.
I wanna see
more of what it showed me.
I can't wait to see it again.
( Soft hum )
¶
( gulps )
( Shuddering )
Lipia: I love you so much...
Milord.
Gabriel: That was incredible.
What a glorious experience.
Even though our fluctlights
are in separate lightcubes,
they connected through
the s.T.L., so when she died,
maybe the release
of quantum data
flowed back to me
by way of that connection.
What am I doing?
Who cares about the how of it?
I've experimented with
so many people since Alicia,
and finally I've experienced
the phenomenon again here.
If that's what
an average a.I. Soul is like
Alice's should be
extraordinary.
Alice, your soul will be sweet,
and I shall relish it.
¶
Dee: Milord,
all preparations are complete.
We are ready
to launch the assault
whenever it pleases you.
Gabriel: Good.
Shasta: The life
of the eastern gate,
which has divided
the human empire
and the land of darkness
since creation,
will expire soon.
Lipia: The five tribes
are excited
about the prospect of war
and the bounty of resources
the human empire contains.
Shasta: And yet,
each integrity knight
is worth a thousand
of our warriors in battle.
The edge we have in our numbers
shall be whittled down
in no time.
Beating them may be possible,
but by the time we do,
we will have suffered
severe losses.
Lipia: If that's true,
it will lead to an imbalance
of power among the tribes.
Shasta: The council of ten
will be powerless,
and the treaty
among the five tribes
will be rescinded.
If that happens,
it will become another age
of blood and iron.
That cannot come to pass.
Our only hope is to make peace
with the human empire.
I must speak with bercouli.
I am certain he would agree
to our request for peace.
But first, I must kill
the one who stands in the way,
emperor vecta.
Gabriel: By the way, last night,
I discovered
an intruder in my chamber.
They had a dagger
hidden in their hair.
( Subjects gasping )
Gabriel: Fear not.
I won't condemn whoever
sent the assassin after me.
( Shasta gasps )
Gabriel: If you wish
to have more power,
there is nothing wrong
using treachery to obtain it,
and if you desire the throne,
feel free to attack me
however you wish.
With that said, if you decide
to embark on such a gamble,
know that the consequences
will be most severe.
For example, this traitor...
( Footsteps scraping )
( Council members gasp )
( Gabriel chuckles )
( Shasta gasps )
¶
( gasps )
Lipia.
We must have peace,
for the sake of all.
That sounds so hypocritical,
especially coming
from the commander
of the dark knights.
Lipia: It is admirable,
and so are you.
( Chuckles )
¶
( sighs ) My lord,
that is why I love you
and always will.
( Shasta gasps )
( Panting )
( Roars )
Fu Za: The poison coursing
through you is so potent,
it can kill a land dragon
with a life of over 30,000
in less than an hour.
( Shasta gasping )
Fu Za: And compared
to your stamina
and total life, you'll be dead
in about three minutes.
( Shasta gasping )
Lipia...
They won't stop me.
¶
( Roars )
( Subjects gasping )
( Fu Za screams )
( Dee groans )
( Shasta roars )
( Subjects gasping )
( Shasta growls )
( Roars )
( Subjects yelling )
( Shasta gasps ) Nothing.
A black void.
Does this man not know life?
( Gasps )
He knows nothing
of the radiance of life,
of love, of the soul.
That's why he seeks
others's souls.
( Gasps )
No matter how powerful
my incarnate ability was,
this man cannot be defeated
by a weapon of murderous intent.
He has a soul, but it is dead.
I'm so sorry, Lipia.
( Council members gasping )
Gabriel: The troops who lost
their commanders shall appoint
whoever is the next highest rank
to lead them.
We will begin the assault
as planned one hour from now.
( Subjects gasping, muttering )
Dee: Long live vecta,
the emperor!
( Subjects cheering )
( Gabriel chuckles )
( Singing in Japanese )
¶
Alice: There it is,
the eastern gate.
Hold here, amayori.
( Gasps )
"Destroyed at the last stage."
We are out of time.