¶
Administrator: Have you ever
felt you were going to die?
Bercouli: Eh?
I don't remember
how long ago it was,
but there was one time.
It was during a fight
with the last general
of the Dark Knights
or the one before.
Didn't think
I'd make it out of that one.
( Administrator laughs )
You did, though.
Eventually you brought
his head back to me.
You felt it then? Never again?
Bercouli: Hmm?
If I did, I don't remember.
Why are you asking?
I doubt someone like you
worries about dyin'. Am I right?
( Administrator chuckles )
Not true, my dear Bercouli.
I feel death hovering over me
every single day.
( Bercouli gasps )
Administrator:
It is there in my dreams
and in the morning
when I awaken.
Why? Because I still
do not control everything,
because I still have
enemies who live
and because, the longer I live,
it is possible that,
at some point in the future,
there will come a new enemy.
( Bercouli chuckles )
Point taken, my lady.
I guess bein' the pontifex
ain't easy after all, huh?
Your eminence, I didn't get
what you meant then,
but I do now.
¶
( chuckles )
( singing in Japanese )
¶
Ronie: Here. Eat up.
I have to say you're looking
much healthier this morning,
kirito.
( Women gasp )
Ronie: And your appetite's
back with a vengeance.
( Women sigh, chuckle )
Alice: Perhaps
spending the night
with four lovely ladies
is the reason.
Asuna: Eh? ( Chuckles )
( Horn blowing )
( Running footsteps )
Bercouli: I'll be damned.
It looks like Emperor Vecta's
got some bold strategies
in mind.
He's taking a risk,
and it's gonna cost him big.
( Alice gasps )
¶
( gasps )
Bercouli: This is war, folks.
I wanna remind you
this ain't the time for mercy.
The enemy's makin' their way
across that canyon Asuna made.
This is our chance to stop 'em.
Alice: Chance?
Bercouli: Yeah.
( Men grunting )
Iskahn: Keep going. Hurry!
( Pugilist gasping )
( Dark Knights groan )
( Dark Knights screaming )
( Iskahn gasps )
( Growls )
Gabriel: I want you
to cast some ropes over
to the other side
and send your people across.
If they fall, they fall.
( Iskahn growls )
Gabriel: Execute anyone
who doesn't comply.
Iskahn: What the hell?
The five tribes should be
conquering the human empire,
not chasing
after some priestess of light.
We're out here
dyin' for nothin'!
Come on, come on. Move it.
Get across while you can.
Hurry, before the enemy notices!
- ( Pugilists panting )
- ( Overlapping chatter )
- Pugilist: Keep pushing!
- ( Iskahn gasps )
( Hooves pounding )
( Gasps )
¶
look out!
The integrity knights
are coming!
Protect the ropes
'til the rest of us get across!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Dark Knights scream )
( Pugilists scream )
Iskahn: Stop it!
Iskahn: This--this ain't no war!
They can't even
defend themselves!
My people trained for this?
To shimmy across a rope
and die for no reason at all?!
¶
forgive me.
( Gasping ) Forgive me.
Gabriel: No doubt about it.
The human empire's a.I.S
are slightly superior
to the dark territory's.
Well done.
As far as adaptability goes,
they're on a whole other level.
You're up, Critter.
Don't blow it.
Critter: And for my next trick,
syncing the Underworld's time
to the real world.
( Chuckles )
Gamer: What?
No way!
Is this for real?
Gamer 2: Are they crazy?
A pvp with
life-like human avatars
and realistic violence?
Gamer 3: You mean
we can like cut off arms
and heads and stuff? No way!
Gamer 4: No restrictions?!
Hell to the yes!
This developer's adventurous!
Gamer 5: Yeah, baby!
I'm so signing up
for this beta!
Critter: Don't push.
There's enough dark knight
accounts for everyone.
Go forth, my dudes, and chop
that human army to ribbons.
Yui: Daddy! Mommy!
I have to do something,
but what?
( Cell phone buzzing )
( Sinon groans )
( Gasps )
¶
Yui: Sinon, it's Yui!
Sinon: Yui? Wh-what are you--
Yui: I'm sorry to call so late,
but it's an emergency!
Get dressed. There's a taxi
waiting out front.
I sent the address and
the fastest route to your phone.
Make sure to follow it!
Sinon: Wh-what's going on?
Where am I going?
Yui: Daddy and mommy
are in danger!
I'll explain on the way!
Leafa: Driver, take me
to minato ward in Tokyo, please.
Sorry I left
without telling you, mom,
but Kazuto's in trouble,
and he needs me.
( Higa snores )
( Gasps )
Hmm?
( Sighs )
It's been ten hours
since Asuna logged in
to the Underworld,
so in there, it's been a year.
What's taking her so long?
( Yawns )
The world's end altar
can't be that far away from her.
Or can it?
- ( Telephone rings )
- ( Gasps )
Hey! Keeks!
- The phone!
- ( Gasps )
Kikuoka: Kikuoka in subcon.
Talk to me.
Man: Hello, sir. I know
I'm not supposed to call hq
unless it's important.
This is Hiraki at Rath Roppongi.
We've got an issue here.
I think
it's some kind of prank.
A couple visitors
just showed up at our location
without an appointment.
Kikuoka: Visitors?
Who are they, clients?
Hiraki: No, they're
definitely not clients,
but they seem to know
a lot about us.
They're girls,
two teenage girls.
Higa and Kikuoka: What?!
Kikuoka: Teenagers, you said?
Hiraki: Yeah.
Anyway, they knew your name
and that you were at rath hq,
so I let them in.
They said I should call you
and ask you
to check the f.L.A. Rate
of the Underworld,
said it was urgent.
( Higa gasps )
Holy...
It--it's one to one?!
Since when?!
Kikuoka: Hey, Hiraki,
did the girls
tell you their names?
Hiraki: Yes, sir,
but the names they gave
are obviously fake.
They said not to worry,
you'd know who they were.
Hold on. I wrote them down.
Let's see.
One called herself "Sinon,"
and the other, "Leafa."
It sounds crazy, but that's
what they told me to tell you.
( Both gasp )
Klein: I swear. He's in a coma,
and he still managed to get
caught up in something crazy.
I mean,
a full-on A.I. Called Alice
who was born in a virtual world
made by the sdf?
( Groans )
This is way beyond v.R. Games,
and there's no goin' back.
Silica: Poor Alice.
She's so special,
and they just want her
to fly fighter jets.
Yui: Ultimately, yes,
but they won't right away.
Rath will probably use her
to demonstrate the technology
to the world first.
The hijackers aboard
the ocean turtle, however,
aren't interested
in demonstrations.
I think, once they get her,
they'll use her
for what she was intended.
Klein: Know anything else
about those creeps,
like who they are
or where they're from?
Yui: I can't confirm it,
but I think they're
U.S. military or intelligence.
- ( Group gasps )
- Klein: What?!
Lisbeth: They're behind it?!
O-Oh, my god.
Yui: Again, I can't confirm
they're involved with this,
but if they are and Alice
does fall into their hands,
they'll use her
for drone warfare.
I know daddy and mommy wouldn't
want that to happen to her,
because Alice--
Alice is proof!
Her existence proves
all v.R. Worlds,
starting with "s.A.O.,"
are real,
that those who lived in them
had real lives!
She's the result of massive
amounts of the time, energy,
and imagination
of thousands of humans!
( All gasp )
Yui: I'm convinced
beyond a doubt
she's why the seed package
was created, its true purpose...
To give birth
to someone like her.
Throughout all
the connected worlds
that sprang up from the seed,
so many people have laughed,
cried, suffered, and loved.
It was the radiance
of all those souls
shimmering with life
that made it possible
for a new form of humanity
to be born in the Underworld.
Daddy and mommy,
Leafa, Klein, Lisbeth,
Silica, Agil, and Sinon,
it's the combination of
your hearts and so many others,
all woven together
in a big tapestry,
that gave birth to Alice!
Lisbeth: Yeah, you're right.
It's all connected,
people and time
and our hearts, too,
flowin' like a big river.
Yui: Eh?
Silica: It's okay, Yui.
Don't cry.
We'll rescue kirito and Asuna.
I promise, we'll do whatever it
takes to get them out of this.
You can count on that.
Klein: Damn straight.
You should have
come to us sooner.
If there's a chance
to get 'em out,
hell, we're taking it.
Agil: You got that right.
I owe 'em as much as anyone.
'Bout damn time
I started paying 'em back.
Yui: You guys!
Thank you so much!
( Laughs )
Seriously, thank you.
Klein: Mm-hmm.
Now the hard part.
There's 30,000
American vrmmo players diving,
and soon it could
go up to 100 thou.
The human army's
just a bunch of targets to them.
Lisbeth: What's stopping us from
doing what the hijackers did?
We can post on the same
U.S. vrmmo sites, too.
We'll tell the players
about the experiment
and the fake beta.
I'm pretty sure they'll listen.
Yui: At the center of it all
is a struggle
for military secrets
between Japan and America.
If we told anyone about that,
it would just make this worse.
Agil: Mm-hmm.
Silica: If we said
they'd be killing
real people,
not avatars, maybe--
oh, who am I kidding?
( Klein scoffs )
Well, I say we tear a page
out of their playbook.
We'll post a notice
for the beta test ourselves.
Then we get the rath guys
to hand out accounts,
and I bet we could get 30,000
or 40,000 logged on, easy.
Agil: That's a great idea, man,
but there's one problem.
Klein: You gonna
tell me what that is?
- Agil: The time.
- ( Klein gasps )
Agil: Here in Japan,
it's 4:30 in the morning.
Besides us, there's not
a whole lot of folks online.
But in Los Angeles,
it's half past noon right now
and 3:30 in New York.
The U.S. has way more
active players online.
( Klein groans )
Yui: Agil is correct about that.
We couldn't get the number
of players we need right now.
It would be
way less than 10,000.
Our accounts would be
the same level as the Americans,
so we'd be evenly matched.
Fighting all of them off
would be impossible.
Lisbeth: But, like, maybe rath
has more god accounts
like the one Asuna's using.
We can't start from scratch.
We'd need as much time as kirito
to level up enough.
Klein: Crap. Game over, then.
- Yui: No.
- ( Both gasp )
Yui: There are strong accounts,
both in terms of level
and in equipment.
The Americans' default accounts
can't compare.
Lisbeth: Really?
How do we get them?
Yui: That's the best part.
The accounts are already yours.
They're the ones
you're logged in with now.
Lisbeth: Huh?
Yui: You must convert them.
If you do, then you
and all the other vrmmo players
you recruit will start
with stronger accounts
than the Americans.
You're all leveled up already.
Just convert, and log in!
Klein: Of course! Why didn't
any of us think of that?!
Yui: Although I should mention
this plan involves some risk.
( Crowd murmuring )
Lisbeth: What i'm
about to tell you
is not some kind of prank.
There's a place
called the Underworld.
It's a virtual world
based on the seed,
made by Japanese researchers.
As I stand here,
tens of thousands
of American players
are logging in to it.
They've been told it's a beta
for a hack-and-slash game
and they can kill
anyone they come across.
But the people
of the Underworld are real.
They're not just npcs.
They're true bottom-up a.I.S
with feelings
and souls like us.
We need your help
to protect them,
but there's no time
to level up there.
But if you convert
your character accounts
to the Underworld,
we can save their people!
( Crowd murmuring )
Sakuya: I know you well,
and I trust your intentions.
You wouldn't have
called us so early
just so you could play
a trick on us.
And the fact kirito hasn't
logged on for over ten days
suggests whatever is going on
is indeed serious.
But a.I.S with human souls
and the U.S. military
out to steal them,
it all seems so far-fetched.
Diving in would be
the only way to confirm it.
In private, you told me
you had other concerns,
that converting our accounts
would have risks.
You should explain
what those are before we decide.
Lisbeth: Sure.
Here's what I know.
The Underworld
isn't a vrmmo game.
It's a simulated civilization,
so you'll be faced with
a few issues once you dive in.
The first one
is there's no user interface
to call up and manipulate.
Once you're logged in,
you can't log yourself out.
( All gasp )
Lisbeth: The only way
for you to log out
is by dying in there.
That brings me to another issue
you all need to know about.
The Underworld doesn't have
a pain absorber function.
( All gasping )
If you take enough damage
to drop your h.P. To zero,
you'll experience
loads of virtual pain.
( All murmuring )
Lisbeth: And finally...
The Underworld's
in a chaotic state right now,
and the devs
can't fully operate it,
so once you convert
your character data
to the Underworld,
there's no guarantee
you'll be able
to convert it back.
And worse, if you die there,
there's a good chance you might
lose your character forever.
Player: Did I hear her right?
Player 2: How can she ask that?
Player 3: Hard pass.
Player 4: Yeah,
what's the point?
Player 5: What a load of crap!
If we help
and lose our characters,
are you gonna
reimburse us for 'em?
Or is this a trick
to weaken the tribes
so you can take over!
Klein: Hey!
Lisbeth: You're wrong.
We're not tricking you!
( All murmuring )
Lisbeth: We know
how hard you worked
to build your characters up,
and no amount of money
can replace their loss.
We're not asking this lightly.
We're begging you to help us.
Right now, our friends are
fighting the American players
alongside the underworlders,
but they're outnumbered,
and they need reinforcements!
Player 5: You're all
"s.A.O." Survivors,
so you should be tough enough
to deal with it!
Screw your sob story!
You think you're all that,
just 'cause
you were in that game!
Well, here's your chance
to prove how bad-ass you are!
Player 6: Why should we care
about hijackers
or a.I.S with souls?
Player 7: Don't bring
this real-life crap
into our game
and expect us to help!
Player 8: You and
the rest of your "s.A.O." Club
can deal with it!
Player 5:
Go save the day again,
you stuck-up jerks!
( Players yelling )
Lisbeth: It didn't work.
No matter what I say,
they don't care.
¶
( Sighs )
( Crowd muttering )
( Lisbeth chuckles )
You're right!
This is a real-life problem!
And as for us survivors,
yeah, some of us
do blur the line
between the real world
and the virtual,
but we don't think we're tougher
or better than anyone here.
None of us think we're heroes!
Me and Silica,
she and I go to a special school
for survivors.
Once a month, the students
have to go to counseling
'cause of the trauma
we still deal with.
They ask us painful questions.
They make some of the kids
take medication,
even though it makes 'em sick.
And the government,
they're afraid of us,
so they monitor us like we're
a bunch of criminals!
The truth is it's not just us
at the returnee school
they're suspicious of.
It's all vrmmo players.
They think we're all
a bunch of deadbeats,
losers dragging society down,
cowards who don't pay taxes
and can't face reality.
People are saying
we need the draft back,
to force us to enlist, 'cause
at least we can be useful there.
And even though
they think that about us,
you know what I believe?
That this here...
This is reality.
( Singing in Japanese )
This world and all the other
virtual worlds connected to it,
they're real.
They're not just games we play.
Here in v.R.,
I have a real life,
and I have real friends.
I laugh, and I cry,
and I feel real feelings,
the same as offline!
Isn't it like that for you?!
We pour our hearts and souls
into this world,
because it's different
from what we got out there!
But if it's all
just a stupid game,
if everything we've been through
and felt here is fake,
if so, then in the end,
what is real for us?!
( Crying )
All the worlds we've grown
fused together.
They're as thick and tall
as the world tree.
And from them...
From them, the Underworld
started to bloom.
I want to protect it.
So please,
please...
Help us.
( Blade slashes )
( Pugilists scream )
Bercouli: Don't stop!
Cut the next one!
( Hooves pounding )
( Asuna gasps )
( Energy pulsing )
( Bercouli gasps )
( Asuna gasps )
¶
( Gabriel chuckles )
( Red Knights yelling )