¶
( Humans and Goblins
yelling and grunting )
Goblin: Hmm?
¶
( Goblins scream )
Fizel: I can't believe Goblins
got this far past our defenses.
Linel: I know, and there
seems to be no end to them.
I think there might be
too many for us to deal with!
Fizel: I bet they're here 'cause
renlicchi abandoned his post.
( Scoffs )
( Goblin yells )
Linel: He probably did,
that coward.
( Renly shudders )
¶
( singing in Japanese )
Renly: I must return
to my station now.
But then...
If I went back,
I'd just be in the way.
Administrator: Renly.
Renly: Mm?
¶
Administrator: Poor child.
It seems that you are broken.
( Renly gasps )
Broken?
Chudelkin: You are a failure!
( Laughs )
Oh, a defective knight!
Administrator:
Renly, I have no choice,
but to punish you
with deepfreeze.
( Renly gasps )
Administrator: Despite
the double-winged blades
choosing you as their master,
you've never achieved perfect
weapon control over them.
As a knight, you are lacking
something most crucial.
Good night, Renly.
( Chudelkin laughs )
Did you hear that?
Her eminence
bade you good night.
Oh, what a lucky boy you are!
I'm so jealous!
¶
Renly: I am a failure.
A fail--
( gasps )
It does not matter
whether I exist or not.
Ronie: What about here?
Tiese: Sure. This tent
looks like it'll be safe enough.
( Renly gasps )
Tiese:
We'll tuck him away in back
and stand guard
at the entrance.
( Ronie sighs )
( Renly gasps )
Tiese: It's so dark.
- ( Rattle )
- ( Gasps )
Is someone there?
- Renly: It is I.
- ( Both gasp )
Renly: I did not mean
to startle you.
Tiese: Uh, sir knight!
- ( Ronie groans )
- Tiese: Forgive our intrusion.
Renly: No. I am at fault here.
And, please, be at ease.
I am no longer a knight.
I am a deserter.
( Both gasp )
Renly: The unit
I was assigned to command
must be in a panic by now.
I am sure some have died.
And yet I hide here in safety
like a filthy coward.
Ronie: Where are my manners?
We haven't
introduced ourselves yet.
My name is Ronie Arabel.
This is Tiese Schtrinen.
And the one behind her...
That's elite disciple Kirito.
Renly: Kirito?
He is the one
who killed the pontifex?
Ronie: Sir knight, forgive me
if I'm being impertinent,
but since you're here,
could you please help us?
We hate to ask, but you see,
we gave our word we'd keep
Kirito safe, no matter what.
( Renly gasps )
Ronie: We're still
primary trainees.
We can't defend ourselves
against things like Goblins yet.
Even so, we accepted
this responsibility.
We have to keep him safe.
Lady Alice is counting on us to.
- ( Man yells )
- ( Body thumps )
- ( All gasp )
- Tiese: Oh, no!
The enemy's already here.
- ( Goblin growls )
- ( Man screams )
( Man gags )
- Tiese: I see smoke.
- Ronie: What?
A-Are they setting
the tents on fire?
- ( Men groaning, yelling )
- Tiese: There's no fire,
just a whole lot
of this weird-looking smoke.
Wait. Now I can see shapes
moving around in it.
( Gasps )
¶
( Ronie whimpers )
( Goblin growls )
Ronie: A Goblin!
- ( Renly gasps )
- Goblin: Looky here!
I found me
some white ium girlies.
( Laughs ) What a lucky day.
Ronie: Tiese.
- ( Goblin chuckles )
- ( Girls shuddering )
( Renly gasping )
Swordsman: I'm going to win
the tournament today, Renly!
Renly: No, I am!
¶
[metal clinks]
Too slow!
( Gasps )
( Swordsman gasps )
¶
( Renly gasping )
( Swordsman gasps ) Renly...
Tiese: S-stay back!
I-I'm warning you!
( Goblin slurps )
So feisty. So tasty!
Tiese: If you come any closer,
I'll kill you!
( Fist creaking )
( Renly gasps )
¶
Are you--
are you trying
to protect these two?
You struggle to,
even though you cannot stand
or speak or draw your sword,
while I cower.
( Sword clangs )
Swordsman: Renly...
( Shuddering )
I want you...
To become a great knight.
Do it for me.
( Gasps )
( Grunts )
- ( Goblin growls )
- ( Girls gasp )
( Goblin gasping )
( Sword clangs )
Both: Huh?
( Renly panting )
Tiese: Sir knight!
You did it! You saved us!
Thank you so much!
( Renly breathes deeply )
Stay here, please,
and protect Kirito.
Both: Y-yes, sir.
¶
Goblins: Eh?
( Goblins growling )
Renly: I am Renly,
integrity knight
Renly synthesis twenty-seven!
If you want my head,
then be ready
to give your lives for it!
Goblin: Chop him to pieces!
( Goblin 2 roars )
( Goblins shriek )
Renly: I can do this.
By now, the smoke should be
clearing from the front lines.
All I have to do
is hold out a little longer,
and help will arrive.
( Metal clangs )
( Gasps )
( Footsteps thudding )
¶
( Kosogi chuckles )
Renly: Are you their commander?
Kosogi: Yeah. I be Kosogi,
chief of the mountain Goblins.
What a shame.
You done killed
some of my best warriors.
Surprised to find ye here...
Ye bein' an integrity knight
and all.
Why ain't you be
where the action is,
with the other knights?
Renly: That is
none of your concern.
Now perish!
( Kosogi chuckles )
( Grunts )
( Renly gasps )
Kosogi: Thought I was just
another Goblin, did ye, boy?
Well, I ain't so impressed
with ye, either, to be honest.
You said before
you were an integrity knight.
I was told one of you
could take on a thousand.
But that ain't the case
for ye, now, is it? ( Chuckles )
That's why ye be hidin'
all the way back here.
Ain't that right?
Administrator: It seems
that you are broken, child.
Renly: Perhaps she was right.
I am a failure.
Maybe I am.
¶
( chuckles ) You are correct.
I am not much of a knight.
Even so, let us be clear.
Though I might be defective,
these are not!
¶
( Kosogi gasps )
Renly: Double wings,
take flight!
( Kosogi growls )
I can do this all day, boy!
Renly: Release...
Recollection!
Beautiful.
Kosogi: Quit playin' around!
( Roars )
( Gags )
- Fizel: Renlicchi?
- Renly: Eh?
¶
( stammers )
Fizel: Well, well, well.
Someone's gotten
a bit more knightly.
We were hoping
to get credit for saving you.
Too bad you had to spoil that.
( Linel sighs )
No one's gonna care
that we chopped off
way more heads than you did.
( Fizel groans )
Both: Sir knight,
we humbly request your orders.
( Renly gasps )
( Clears throat )
Very well, then.
Keep Kirito and the girls safe.
Fizel: You don't
have to worry about that.
We handed them all off
to the supply corps just now.
( Renly sighs )
We should secure the area, then.
Linel: We killed
all the Goblins here.
( Renly gasps )
I-If  that is the case,
then I suppose
we'd best return to our units.
Fizel: Yes, sir.
Linel: As you command.
Renly: Thank you.
Mage: Lord Sigurosig,
Lord Shibori, and Lord Kosogi
have all been killed.
Dee: Useless wretches.
Demi-Humans can't be
counted on for anything.
Have you located
all the integrity knights yet?
Mage: Currently
we have the three
on the front lines
in our sights.
We found two more
among their rear units,
but we do not
have a fix on them yet.
Dee: There are
only five knights here?
Impossible, unless that is
all they ever had.
Regardless of how many
there are here,
we must slaughter them all.
Go on. Wake the minions.
Have them fly for 700 mels,
then descend
upon the battlefield...
And kill everything.
Mage: Forgive the question,
but won't our Demi-human units
get caught in that?
- Dee: Too bad.
- Mage: Right.
How many minions do you wish?
We have 800 available.
They are all
hatched and ready to go.
Dee: Hmm.
( Slurps )
Send every last one of them.
( Minion roars )
Bercouli: Here they come.
¶
Time-splitting sword!
( Chorus vocalizing )
Air slice!
( Growls )
Alice: Uncle activated
his perfect weapon control.
He has made his move.
¶
( No audible dialogue )
Dee: You imbecile!
How did we not know
they had
such a large unit of mages?
- Mage: Th-they don't.
- ( Dee sputtering )
Mage: I-I don't know
what happened.
( Dee breathes deeply )
Have they deployed
their flying dragons yet?
Mage: No.
The skies above the battlefield
are clear.
Not one dragon has been spotted.
Dee: Then there can be
only one explanation for it.
That must be
perfect weapon control,
their knight's special skill.
Damn them.
( Scoffs ) They are
stronger than I thought.
Using a weapon that way
is risky, though.
It would drain massive amounts
of the knight's life.
How could they unleash
such a barrage?
Mage: I just got word, milady.
Our spotters located
the two knights in the rear.
We've targeted them.
We now have all five of them
in our sights.
Dee: Good.
I have waited for this.
It is my chance for glory,
and I shall seize it.
( Sighs )
Ogre archers and dark mages,
advance into the ravine!
Once you are in position,
ready the bows, and begin
the incineration incantation!
¶
Arch Mage: Mage unit...
Prepare for wide-range
incineration projectiles!
Spotters, begin the incantation
to guide the projectiles
to the integrity knight's
position!
Ogres, prepare to fire!
¶
( soldier gags )
( soldier 2 groans )
Alice: Why is it...
That the souls
of the fallen below,
whether human or Demi-human,
generate sacred power
that is so warm and pure?
The people of the human empire
and the monsters
of the dark territory
have essentially the same souls.
The only difference
is whether they were born
on one side of the end mountains
or the other.
If so, then why are they--
why are we fighting?
Kirito, if you were here...
No. I raised my sword
against the pontifex
and defied the axiom church.
It is my duty
to see this through now.
( Amayori trills )
¶
Alice: They're here.
As far as maintaining elements,
I am no match for what thousands
of dark mages are capable of,
and converting sacred power
into fire or ice elements
would not be
a potent enough art
to sap all the spatial resources
rising from the ravine.
However...
Sealing luminous elements
inside a mirror
would reflect them infinitely,
Mages: System call!
Generate thermal element!
( Mages gasping )
( Arch Mage gasping )
System call!
Generate thermal element!
( Gasps )
Mage: It's not working.
What's going on?
Mage 2: What'll we do? We can't
activate the projectiles
without thermal elements!
Arch Mage: Damn! Why isn't
the incantation working?
Mage 3: Arch Mage, if I may,
I think all the spatial
resources have been depleted.
Arch Mage: What?!
Are you insane?!
That's impossible!
What about all the screaming?
Scores of both Humans and
Demi-Humans have died already!
If those resources aren't here,
then where did they all go?!
Alice: The burden
of taking countless lives
for the sake of one
shall be mine to bear.
Bloom, flowers!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Inhales )
Burst element.
( Lava bubbling )
( Singing in Japanese )
¶