Alice: Burst element.
( Mages yelling )
Mage: Wh-what do we do?!
( Mages screaming )
( Dee gasps )
Mage 2: For some reason,
there was a lack
of spatial power,
and we couldn't conjure
our incineration projectiles,
and then the enemy
launched a large-scale attack.
90% of the Demi-human unit,
70% of the Ogre Archers,
and over 30% of the Dark Mage
unit were destroyed.
Dee: "For some reason"?
Are you dense?!
Someone used
a massive formal art
and drained all
the spatial power in the ravine!
But how can that be?
I can't even conjure
a spell of that scale.
Who do they have
that is that powerful?
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( army yelling, cheering )
( Applause )
Fanatio: Welcome back.
You did well.
( Gasps )
The enemy has retreated.
You guided us to victory.
Alice: No, Fanatio.
This battle
is far from being over.
More sacred power
has collected in the ravine.
We must consume it
with healing arts
before the enemy can absorb it.
Time is short,
and we have yet to face
their dark knights
and pugilists.
Fanatio: True.
All who are able,
take the wounded, and fall back!
Priests, focus on healing
until all the spatial power
has been depleted!
And keep watch
for enemy movement!
I will go and
give my report to the commander.
Will you be all right here?
Alice: Mm-hmm.
I could not have succeeded
without you, Amayori.
Eat your fill,
and get some rest.
You've earned it.
( Amayori trills )
( Wings flapping )
Eldrie: Milady.
Alice: Eh?
( Gasps ) Eldrie!
Have you been injured?
Eldrie: No.
Nothing major, at least.
But if I am being honest,
I would have preferred
to perish.
Alice: What kind
of talk is that?
Your troops look up to you,
and you have a duty
to lead them
and fight to the very end.
Eldrie: And yet,
as a leader, I have failed.
( Shuddering )
Not only did
the goblins breach my ranks,
their commander
was felled by Sir Renly.
How humiliating.
I betrayed your teachings
and your expectations of me.
To think I could be worthy
of her heart, her love,
how laughable!
I do not have the right
to call myself your disciple!
Alice: Of course you do.
I know you did all you could.
Can you not see
how much everyone needs you--
the troops under your command,
the citizens,
I, too, as a matter of fact.
Eldrie: Do you?
For my strength
on the battlefield?
Nothing more?
- ( Male groaning )
- ( Both gasp )
¶
( groaning continues )
( Alice gasps )
Alice: Stop right there!
What business
do you have here unarmed?
Your life is almost at its end.
Furgr: I be Furgr.
I be Chief of all Ogre.
Alice: Keep up your guard.
He is one
of their council of ten.
Furgr: I saw all.
The light and fire,
you conjure, unleash.
Your power, your look,
you be Priestess of Light.
If take back with me,
end of war,
ogre return to plains.
Alice: Priestess? End of war?
Who told you this?
Come on now. Speak up.
Eldrie: Milady, this fiend
is obviously stalling!
( Furgr growls )
( Eldrie yells )
( Gasps )
But, milady,
he lies!
Alice: As you say,
I am the Priestess of Light.
Now, then,
before I go anywhere with you,
I wish to know
who it is that seeks me.
Furgr: Emperor Vecta.
( Alice gasps )
Furgr: He say
find Priestess of Light.
He grant wish
to who catch and bring to him,
and then ogre can go home,
raise horses,
hunt bird, and live.
Alice: Surely you
must despise me.
Do you not wish to avenge
your people? I killed them.
Furgr: Burden of strong
heavy as they be strong.
I Chief.
My burden to protect kind.
Is why I have no choice.
I catch you and take back!
( Roaring )
¶
Alice: May your soul
return home,
back to the plains.
Emperor Vecta.
Gabriel: Hmph. So the reason
your strategy failed
and a thousand dark mages died
was because the enemy
absorbed all the spatial power
before you could.
Did I understand that correctly?
Dee: Yes.
Y-Your majesty,
I-I swear we had no idea
they had someone
who could cast such an art,
only the pontifex,
and she is dead.
Gabriel: Is there some other way
to replenish this power?
Dee: Yes,
using spatial resources,
such as rich land and sunlight,
but to generate enough power
to destroy the enemy,
we would need ample amounts,
and unfortunately
there is little here.
Gabriel: Obviously.
In fact,
I see no grass or trees at all,
and the sun set a while ago.
So tell me,
what were you going to use
as a power source
for your attack spell?
Dee: Well, each life has power,
and during the assault,
as warriors
from both sides died,
their expired lives filled
the air with spatial power.
Gabriel: Ah.
( Dee sobbing )
¶
Gabriel: Blood and life.
( Dee gasps )
( Whimpers )
Gabriel: Dee Eye Ell,
would 3,000 be sufficient?
Dee: Uh, what?
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
Yes, your majesty.
That would be enough.
( Soft chatter )
Bercouli: "Priestess of Light"?
Alice: Yes. I do not recall
reading about this person
in any of the history books,
but whoever she may be,
the emperor of
the dark territory is after her.
( Bercouli grunts )
This emperor...
Is the Dark God Vecta, huh?
Fanatio: A god walking among us?
I find that hard to believe.
Bercouli: All right, kid.
Let's say Vecta's back
and running things
in the dark territory.
If what the ogre said's true
and Vecta's looking
for this Priestess of Light
and he thinks you're it,
how's that gonna affect
where this war goes from here?
Alice: The five tribes
want the resources
of the human empire. However...
Vecta just wants
the Priestess of Light.
I have a plan.
I shall enter
the dark territory,
then make my way
to the edge of it.
If the Priestess of Light
is what Vecta wants,
then he will come after me
with most of his army.
The troops he leaves behind
will be without leadership,
and you can wipe them out
in the chaos.
Then I shall make my way
to the world's end altar.
Kikuoka: All right,
once we're off the line,
I'll crank the F.L.A. To 1,000.
Then take Alice, and head
to the world's end altar!
Kirito: I never
heard of that place!
Kikuoka: That's okay!
Just go out the eastern gate,
and the altar's due south.
Alice: Perhaps, if I go there...
( Bercouli sighs ) All right,
but I'm sending a third
of our troops along with you.
Alice: Uncle...
You cannot spare that many
just for my escort.
Bercouli: The enemy
has more than 30,000 left.
They're not all gonna chase you,
especially if you're
the only one running around.
If the plan is to get them
to split their ranks,
we gotta give 'em
a big enough reason to.
Alice: You have a point.
Bercouli: I got
one more condition for you.
Alice: What is it?
Bercouli: The only way
you're doing this
- is if I come along.
- Alice: Huh?
( Bercouli chuckles )
Dee: Orc chief Lilpilin,
you will offer 3,000 lives
so that my dark mages
can launch their attack spell.
( Lilpilin gasps )
Y-You can't do that to us!
My tribe are warriors,
and we came here to fight!
You and your people failed,
so why do we have to pay
for that with our lives?!
Dee: This is an order
from the emperor.
( Lilpilin growls )
- Orc: Lil!
- ( Lilpilin gasps )
Orc: We have no choice,
'cept to obey
his majesty's orders.
Lilpilin: But, Lenju--
Lenju: If he needs
3,000 of our troops,
I'll offer my life
and my clan's.
I'll do it for him
and for the honor of the orc.
( Lilpilin groans )
Lenju: Lil...
You know what I believe.
All souls go to heaven.
Be it human or orc,
when we die, we go there.
And that's where I'll
be waiting for you.
( Lilpilin sobs )
I know, Len. I know.
I'm sorry I can't stop this!
( Dee groans )
You will assemble your troops
100 mels from the ravine,
3,000, not one less.
Do it now.
( Lilpilin growls )
¶
Bercouli: Right. Move out!
( Soldiers yelling )
Alice: Eldrie.
Our goal is to split
the enemy forces
and destroy the group
that follows us.
After we pass
through the eastern gate,
the guard unit,
the priest unit,
and the supply corps
will head south.
If the terrain is favorable,
the troops will take position.
Until then, we knights
will act as a diversion.
( Fanatio breathes deeply )
Return to your positions,
and prepare for battle!
¶
Mages: System call.
Transfer human unit durability,
area to self.
Generate umbral element.
- Form element.
- ( Lilpilin gasping )
Mages: Worm shape.
( Orcs groaning, wailing )
( Lilpilin shuddering )
Orcs: Long live the Orc Tribe!
Glory be to the Orc!
( Gagging )
( Wailing )
( Lenju groans )
( Lilpilin gasps ) Lenju!
( Lenju sighs )
( Lilpilin crying )
Damn humans.
Damn them all.
( Sobbing )
A curse on every one of them.
( Wind blowing )
Mages: Transfer
human unit durability.
- Alice: It can't be.
- Mages: Area to self.
Alice: They are
chanting a sacred art.
Uncle! I used
all the spatial resources here.
There should not be enough left
to carry out a large-scale art!
( Bercouli gasps )
There is. They're making it.
( Deathworms wailing )
( Dee laughs )
What incredible power.
How magnificent.
So much darkness.
So much potential.
( Sighing )
( Laughs )
Mage: I just got word
from our spotters.
There are
integrity knights approaching.
Dee: This Deathworm attack spell
can't be blocked
by sword or armor.
Those damned integrity knights
will be devoured alive!
Be patient!
Let them get closer!
Hold. Hold.
Now, fire!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Bercouli gasps )
( Growls )
We're gonna lure 'em away.
Pull up!
Damn it.
No, kid!
Your sword won't work!
Alice: Eldrie!
Eldrie: Hup!
Alice:
What are you doing, Eldrie?!
Eldrie: Divine serpent of yore,
if you are truly
the king of snakes,
then you should have no trouble
devouring this pack
of Earthworms!
( Grunts )
( Alice gasps )
Eldrie: Release recollection!
( Bercouli groans )
( Chorus vocalizing )
Eldrie: This way,
you disgusting things!
( Deathworms squealing )
( Eldrie grunts )
( Groaning )
( Screaming )
( Gasps )
( Yells )
No. I shall not give up,
not yet!
( Groans )
Lady Alice.
( Squelch )
Alice: Eldrie!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Alice yells )
Eldrie!
E-Eldrie!
Please, open your eyes!
Don't die. You cannot leave me,
not like this! Do you hear?!
( Crying )
Eldrie: You're safe, milady?
Alice: Yes. Yes, I am,
thanks to you.
Don't go. I meant it
when I said I need you!
Eldrie: Do not cry, milady.
You must think
of those who need you.
They are all
that matter now, not I.
I have behaved so selfishly.
I thought I could
have you all to myself.
Alice: That does not matter.
Just stay!
You are my disciple!
I will give you
whatever you wish!
Eldrie: No.
I have all that I need.
( Alice gasps )
Eldrie! Eldrie!
Eldrie: Do not cry...
Mother.
( Alice gasps )
( Takiguri keening )
Alice: Eldrie.
I swear to you...
They shall pay
for what they've done!
Amayori, takiguri...
Charge the enemy.
( Chorus vocalizing )
Dee: No! It can't be!
At that priority level,
the Deathworms
should have easily devoured
the integrity knights
and the ground troops!
What kind of art
did those rotten humans use?
( Gasps )
Retreat! Hurry! Fall back!
( Mages screaming )
Alice: Burn them. Burn them all!
( Dee screams )
( Groans )
Alice: Enhance armament.
( Dee wails )
No! I can't die,
not here, not like this!
I'm going to be the empress.
I'm supposed to become
the ruler of this world!
( Squelch )
Mage: M-Milady.
Mage 2: We've done
nothing wrong!
Dee: System call!
( Chorus vocalizing )
Alice: I am Alice,
Integrity Knight
Alice Synthesis Thirty!
I am the proxy
of the three goddesses
who protect this realm!
I am the Priestess of Light,
and whoever dares defy me...
( Through skull )
Shall know the fury of my power!
( Gabriel gasps )
Alice.
( Chuckles )
Alicia.
( Singing in Japanese )
¶