Asuna: I got this!
( Kirito yells )
Player: Well,
that's the end of that.
All teams, retreat.
Grid one-nine's too hot.
Player #2: Aw, we could
have killed 'em all
if we stuck with it.
You sure you wanna
end the day like this, boss?
Player #1: That team's
all over the place.
Fighting them
won't help with our training.
We have a big mission coming up,
and we need to stay sharp.
Let's go.
( Man sighs ) Hmm?
Woman: Mr. Miller, the people
from the N.S.A. Are here.
Miller: Send them in, please.
Agent: Mr. Miller,
we'd like to retain the services
of glowgen defense systems
for a top-secret mission.
Miller: What is the nature
of the mission?
Agent: To acquire a piece
of tech called soul translation.
Miller: I'm not familiar
with what that is.
Agent: A Japanese company
called rath developed it.
It's a machine
capable of analyzing a soul.
Miller: A human soul?
That's hard to believe.
Agent: Yes, well,
it's been verified.
With this soul translation tech,
not only can rath
scan and read a soul,
they can clone it.
The project is code-named Alice,
and its goal is to develop
an artificial soul
to pilot military drones.
That kind of tech
would disrupt the balance
of power in east Asia.
Agent 2: Needless to say,
the U.S. is concerned
and wants to keep that
from happening.
Miller: Understandable.
Please go on.
What are the specifics
of the mission?
Agent 2: There's a mega-float
moored near the izu islands.
It's called the ocean turtle.
We need you
to infiltrate the facility,
secure
the soul translation tech,
and bring it back.
Miller: So you want to raid
a Japanese vessel,
one of our allies.
Agent 2: We have
a contact inside the J.S.D.F.
They'll be sure
to leave the window
open for you on the day.
Use whatever methods you want.
Just keep in mind
this is off the books.
You won't get any support
from the U.S. if you get caught.
Miller: All right, then.
I'll assemble a team
and lead this mission myself.
( Chuckles ) Alice.
Your soul will be sweet,
maybe the sweetest yet.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
- ( Thump )
- Miller: Hmm?
Merc: Say that again, critter.
I dare you.
Critter: Sure, Vassago,
but it won't change a thing.
The lock on this system's
tougher than dried shit.
I could try and crack it
with the laptop we brought,
but you'd die of old age
before I got in.
They boned us, and there's
nothing I can do about it.
Vassago: That ain't
all you said,
you four-eyed scumbag.
You said, "we wouldn't
be stuck like this
if we weren't so slow
getting in here."
Critter: So what if I did?
I was just pointing out
the facts, is al--
Vassago: Next time, instead of
waiting for the all-clear,
you're coming up front
with us, you pussy.
( Fingers snap )
Miller: Enough.
You boys better cool down.
This isn't the time to start
pointing fingers at each other.
We have to figure out
how to deal with the situation.
Vassago: Aw, come on, bro!
Let me put this worm
in his place.
Miller: I said stand down.
Everyone did
what they were supposed to.
Aside from Gary getting winged
by a round, the team's intact.
And now that we're
in the control room,
we're exactly where
we need to be to get this done.
Vassago: Get what done?
If we can't get
access to the system,
then we can't get
what we came here to get.
The schematics said
everything's automated,
and the lightcube cluster
thing's behind a wall of steel.
Miller: Right.
So, all we have to do now
is figure out a way
to breach that wall.
Vassago: Yeah, well,
the S.D.F. Agents onboard
ain't gonna hide
in their holes forever.
And, when that ship outside
figures out what's what,
we'll be up to our ass
in soldiers.
Miller: The client told me
they have a special
relationship with the J.S.D.F.
They assured me
we'd have a 24-hour window
before the ship rolled in.
Critter: Ooh! Espionage!
That's way better than
a boring old smash-and-grab.
( Miller chuckles ) All right.
Let's go over the situation.
We stormed the facility
40 minutes ago.
Right now,
it's 14:47, local time.
We're standing
in the main control room
of the ocean turtle.
We've been locked
out of the system,
and we were unable to capture
any rath staff
to help us unlock it--
a minor setback,
not the end of the world.
Our new objective is to
infiltrate the sub control room
and try from there.
Well, Brigg?
Do you think it's possible
to cut through
the bulkhead door?
Brigg: Not with
the kind of gear we brought.
It's made out of some kind
of rock-hard composite material.
If we gotta be
out of here in 24,
the portable saw ain't enough.
We need something
bigger and sharper.
Miller: All right.
Hans, can we use C-4 to blow it?
Hans: Sure,
but I wouldn't recommend it.
The chamber
with the lightcube cluster
is supposed to be
on the other side
of the wall there.
If we blow the door,
we'd risk damaging the chamber
and everything in it.
Miller: Hmm.
All right, somehow we
have to find one lightcube
in a vault of thousands
and retrieve it.
We have the cube's I.D.
As long as we have
a working console,
we can eject it
along with its interface.
Vassago: Piece of cake.
Thank god we brought seﾑor dork
along for the ride.
All that bs
about hacking the Pentagon.
If you were really that good,
you would have
had this system open by now.
Critter: Listen
to the super soldier.
Up to now,
the only combat you've seen's
been the virtual kind, hoss.
( Vassago growls ) Goddamn nerd!
( Both gasp )
Miller: Do you want
to go back empty-handed
and, instead of a big,
fat bonus, get laughed at?
Vassago: Hell, no.
Miller: And how about you?
Are you gonna let
some amateur programmers
lock you out?
Critter: No.
Miller: Then, think, damn it!
Come up with a way to get in
and prove you got
more than oatmeal
in your skulls. Understood?!
Mercs: Yes, sir!
¶
Miller: The pressurized bulkhead
leading to the lightcube cluster
can't be breached.
We have to find some other way
to access it from here.
What you got?
Critter: Admin privileges
can't unlock the system.
All I can do is bring up
a visual of the world
so we can see what
all the fluctlights are doing,
basically, watch 'em
living their lives
in their little
fairy-tale kingdom.
Miller: Goblins?
Critter: You know
your fantasy tropes, captain.
Vassago: They seem kinda big
for regular goblins.
Yeah. Those things
are hobgoblins.
Miller: Critter.
Critter: Hmm. Yeah?
Miller: Are those creatures
part of the system,
like NPCs?
Critter: Mm-mmm.
Not according
to what I'm seeing.
Check it out. They all got
their own lightcube designation,
which means
they're in the cluster.
Those things all have souls.
Vassago: You're kidding!
Those hobgoblins
have human souls, same as us?
Yo, check out
what the other lightcubes got!
Like, maybe they're all filled
with goblin and orc souls, too!
Maybe Alice is one!
Critter: Would you chill?
Look at the screen.
The underworld is split
into the human empire,
where, you know, humans live.
And, surrounding that,
on the other side
of the mountains,
is the dark territory,
where the monsters are.
With a name like Alice,
I'm pretty sure
she's both a she and human.
The problem is,
the human part is so big
and filled with people,
we'll never find her like this.
Vassago: Not sitting out here,
that's for sure.
But, in there, we could.
If they got a civilization,
they can talk,
so just drop me in,
and I can ask around
'til I find her.
Critter: Good idea!
For a dumb-ass.
Vassago: You little bastard!
Critter: Stop and think.
There's tens
of thousands of people
living in the human empire.
It's huge,
and you're just one person.
- You can't ask every...One.
- Vassago: Huh?
Critter: Unless...
You're someone with some clout.
Miller: Good point.
The researchers
must have special accounts
they could use to log in there.
It's a safe bet those accounts
would be a higher level
than the average citizen.
Isn't that right, critter?
Critter: Yeah, boss. Exactly!
Out of all the ranks
and classes,
the rath peeps
had to set aside a few to use.
That way, they could monitor
and tweak the world
from inside.
Vassago: Uh-huh.
Now we're talking.
Hey, how 'bout
if I log in as a general
or president
or something like that?
I'd give the order to find Alice
and let the grunts do the work.
Critter: Oh, my god.
Now that I hear you say it,
I'm not so sure
I'm a fan of the idea anymore.
Eh, balls.
They got
all these high-level accounts
locked down
as tight as the system.
If we dive in
to the human empire,
it's gonna be as
a plain old, low-level person.
Vassago: Damn it.
So much for that idea.
Miller: No. Try again,
but, this time, search
for any high-level accounts
outside the human empire.
Critter: Outside it?
Okay, but the chances
of Alice being in monster land
is close to nil.
Miller: Yes, I'm aware of that.
But, if all that separates
the two regions are mountains,
they can be crossed.
Vassago: Yeah!
That's why you're in charge!
Always thinking outside the box.
I can see it now.
I'll dive in as a boss monster
and lead a raid on the humans.
( Chuckles )
I'd be down with that.
( Critter whistles ) Look!
I think I found
a couple contenders.
No password required, gents.
Specs look good.
This one's classified
as a dark knight.
So edgy.
And his
object control level's at 70.
He's a bad-ass to the bone!
Vassago: Sweet.
Right up my alley.
Yo, I got dibs
on the dark knight.
I found another account
that we can access.
Eh? Well, that's weird.
There's no rank, and it
doesn't have a level, either,
no durability,
system control authority.
The only setting is its name,
emperor vecta.
Vassago: Hell, yeah. That guy's
the king of the monster world.
Changed my mind. I'll be him.
- Miller: No.
- Vassago: Eh?
Miller: I'll use that account.
Vassago: All right, bro.
You're the emperor,
and I'm cool
being a dark knight.
Let's get this show
on the road.
I wanna chop some fools
with my sword!
Come on, four eyes.
What do we gotta do to log in?
( Critter sighs )
Miller: Speak up, critter.
Something's obviously
bothering you.
Critter: Maybe i'm
just being overcautious,
but I keep seeing the same term
pop up again and again
in these logs.
It might not affect our op,
but still...
Miller: Go on.
What is this term?
Critter: "The final load test."
Higa: How do I put this?
As far as kirito's
real-world condition,
it's like I said before.
Things aren't
looking too good for him.
The only thing
that gives me hope
is he's still logged in
to the underworld.
That's good. See, even though
his self-image is damaged,
his fluctlight's still active
and receiving stimuli,
so there's a chance
his neural network can heal.
I was thinking.
His guilt
over losing his friends
is what damaged his soul, right?
What if--
and it's a big what if.
What if someone forgave him?
That might help.
Kikuoka: Huh?
Asuna: Send me. I'll go.
Rinko: A-Asuna.
Asuna: I'll go.
Log me in to the underworld.
I want to tell him
that he did all he could...
That it's okay,
that, after all the pain
and sadness I know he suffered,
in the end,
he did the best he could.
Kikuoka: All right.
We have another S.T.L.
We can use.
But the underworld's
at a critical stage.
It's not exactly stable
right now.
It's scheduled to enter
the final load test soon,
the last phase
of the experiment.
Rinko: Final load test?
What happens then?
Higa: The eastern gate
separates the human empire
from the dark territory.
Once its durability level
hits zero,
the monsters
will invade the human side.
If the humans were able to
build up their defenses in time,
they could drive the monsters
back to their side,
but now it's up in the air.
Kirito pretty much destroyed
the Axiom Church,
the ruling body there,
so who knows
what'll happen now?
Kikuoka: At this point,
having someone dive in there
might be the best course
of action for all our concerns.
Once the invasion begins,
there's no telling how chaotic
the underworld will get,
and there's a good chance
Alice could be killed.
But, if we send someone in
using a high-level account,
they could find Alice and
have the power to keep her safe
long enough to get her
to the world end's altar.
Then, using the terminal there,
they can eject her lightcube
to this control room.
Rinko: Ah! So that's
why you told kirito
to take her there, to eject her.
( Kikuoka sighs )
He'd have gotten her there
by now if he were able to.
You heard what he said.
She was right there with him.
Rinko: Time there's accelerated,
so, by now, months have passed.
Do you think there's a chance
they're still together,
even now?
Higa: I'd say
it's a good bet they are.
And personally, I think,
if anyone's gonna dive in,
it should be Asuna.
She's our best hope
at breaking through to kirito.
Plus she's got
the combat skills
to protect Alice
and get her to the terminal.
Kikuoka: You don't need
to convince me about that.
All right, let's find her
a high-level account
to dive in with.
Higa: Sure thing.
I got tons of options.
A knight, a general, a noble--
whatever you pick's
gonna have high stats, Asuna.
Rinko: Wait.
I just thought of something.
Higa: What is it?
Rinko: What about
the people in main con?
If they're here for Alice,
maybe they've got
the same idea we do.
Higa: Yeah. Maybe.
There's two S.T.L's over there
they can use.
Thing is, the passwords I set
for the high-level accounts
are tough, and they
won't have time to crack 'em.
If they dive in, they can
only go as a level-one person--
- ( sighs )
- Rinko: What's wrong?
Higa: Oh--
nah, it's nothing.
¶
Aki: Are you ready for this?
Asuna: Yeah.
Ready as I'll ever be.
( Sinon breathing softly )
( Gasping )
( Gunshot )
( Clears rifle chamber )
¶
( Footstep echoes )
( Gasps )
( Wind blowing )
( Sighs )
( Gasps )
¶
( yelps )
( Groans )
( Miller chuckles )
( Sinon gasps )
Miller: Your soul...
Will be so sweet.
( Sinon gagging )
¶
( Gasps )
Jeez, not him again.
( Cell phone buzzes )
Asuna.
Yui: Hi, Sinon.
I have to tell you
and the others
something important.
Could you please
log in to "A.L.O." Right away?
( Sinon sighs )
Yui: It's risky,
but there's a chance
Daddy's fluctlight
can be repaired,
so Mommy dove in
to the underworld to save him.
Leafa: I hope she can.
Silica: What if she can't?
Lisbeth: Ah, would you guys
stop worrying?
Kirito's always
pulled through before.
Sinon: This sucks.
I can't stand
that they're stuck out there.
- ( Silica sighs )
- Sinon: And those hijackers,
what if they figure out
how to get to them?
Klein: There's gotta be
something we can do,
'cept sit around and wait.
( Yui sighs )
They're safe for now.
But be ready.
If worse comes to worse,
I'll be calling on you for help.
¶
Critter:
Fasten your seat belts, gents.
( Miller sighs )
( Wind blowing )
Lipia: Thank you
for seeing me, milord.
I, Lipia Zancale, bring news.
Lord: Very good. Take a seat.
Lipia: Thank you, milord.
Shasta: Don't be so formal.
It's just us here.
Lipia: Yes, I know,
but officially
I'm still on duty.
( Shasta sighs )
Have it your way.
Your familiar warned
of an impending emergency.
Is it that serious?
Lipia: Yes, quite serious.
The Pontifex
of the Axiom Church is dead.
( Shasta gasps )
That immortal being?
Lipia: Yes. I, too,
found it hard to believe,
so I spent the past week
confirming it.
Shasta: I see.
Perfect.
Lipia: I-I'm sorry.
Perfect for--
shasta: For peace,
peace for all.
Lipia: Is that still possible?
Do you honestly
believe that, milord?
Shasta: Whether it's
possible or not,
it must be achieved,
no matter what.
Lipia: But, milord,
you would first have to convince
the other nine in the council,
and, well, would
the order of Integrity Knights
even entertain
peace negotiations with us?
Shasta: Yes.
I believe the Integrity Knights
would be interested.
If the Pontifex is dead,
then I'd wager old man Bercouli
is in command now.
I can't stand him,
but he is reasonable.
I hate to say this,
but the only thing that could
get in the way of peace talks
would be our council of ten,
not all, just four of them.
They will have to die.
Lipia: Milord! That's too risky!
You could handle
the goblin chiefs
and the Orc Chief. However--
Shasta: The head
of the dark mages guild
would be difficult. I know.
She hopes to find the secret
to administrator's immortality
and one day become empress.
Peace would get in the way
of her ambitions.
Lipia: Precisely!
That is why you cannot
take the chance, milord.
As I said, the Goblin and
Orc Chiefs are no match for you,
but she is diabolical!
I can't imagine
what kind of evil spells
she has up her sleeve!
( Singing in Japanese )
( Shasta chuckles )
Listen, Lipia,
how long have you and I
been together?
Lipia: Uh...
Well, um...
Since I turned 21, I think,
so four years now?
Shasta: That long? Really?
Forgive me.
I made you wait far too long.
It's not fair.
I was thinking...
Maybe now we could...
You know...
Make it official
and become husband and wife.
( Lipia gasps )
- Milord.
- Shasta: I know.
I wish I were younger, too.
¶
- Man: Emergency!
- Lipia: I--
Man: It's an emergency!
Come to the throne room!
The chain that seals the door
is trembling!
¶
( Miller chuckles )