( both yelping )
I could not hate
baths any more.
Hey, Shiro, how am I
supposed to wash you
if you keep squirming?
Come on, sis,
after all the craziness
that went down today,
I'd say a bath
is definitely in order.
Just go with it.
I hate taking baths 'cause
it makes my hair stiff.
If that's the case, why don't
you try some of my shampoo?
( screams )
W‐where'd the hell'd
you come from, Jibril?!
Suffering from tired,
dried‐out hair?
Get soft, silky,
flowing tresses
with Flugel's very own
Spirit Water Blend.
And as a bonus, I,
Jibril, your new slave,
will even throw in a free
back scrubbing for my Masters.
Let me explore
those hot alien bodies.
Shiro, watch out!
Her very existence
is 18 and over!
Jibril, wait.
Oh!
You just sit there
and watch, naughty girl.
What? That's not fair.
The stupid steam's covering up
all the good stuff.
Look at that, already bossing
her around like a pro.
You've really made
your big brother proud,
learning to crack the whip
at such a young age.
I really hate the fact
that I'm starting
to get used
to this crap.
Steph:
Uh, what in
the world is this?
I prepared it for my Masters.
I do believe in your country
they call a kitchen.
Um, excuse me, Steve‐
It's Steph!
My name is Stephanie Dola.
Well, "Dola" is ugly,
and I don't care
for you much anyway,
so I'm going to call you
something easier to remember
like Dolly.
UGH! Dolly?!
By the way, I received
a message from Sora.
"Looks like there's plenty
of sugar and butter here,
so feel free to bake
whatever you want."
Message ends.
Steph:
Really?
Oh, think of all the desserts
I can make with this.
Ohh! Hold on, that's just
their backhanded way
of getting me to bake
goodies for them.
Why do they always try to take
advantage of poor little me?
But if it weren't for you,
we would have lost.
Thanks a lot, Steph.
( squeals )
I'm on it!
So this is how the lowly
Imanity experience
that strange feeling
called love, isn't it?
Huh? Love?
No, no, no, you're wrong!
I believe you were ordered
to fall in love,
not stay in love...
so what's the deal, Dolly?
Why do you still seem to be
so affected by it, hmm?
At first, I thought
you were useless,
but your clownish behavior
is actually quite amusing.
( leaves rustle )
Greetings, Kurami,
I'm finally back.
You wanted some
information, right?
Or was it food?
Wait, I know.
How about me?
( laughs )
Thanks, but I'll take
my clothes first.
Mm, this is great.
We had that poor girl you beat
in the tournament to thank.
Ever since she started enacting
the new King's policies,
the quality of life in Elkia
has really started to improve.
Whatever.
Little Princess. Hmph.
She's just the puppet
of a puppet,
and as shameless as her
grandfather was foolish.
I know you feel guilty
for trying to cheat her
out of the kingdom,
and I know you've been working
on an apology when you didn't
think I was watching.
You're so adorable, Kurami.
Hey, how'd you‐
I mean, more importantly,
don't you have
any intel to report?
Oh, well, this and that.
It seems that the new King
has somehow acquired a Flugel
as a personal slave
and he's really interested
in the Eastern Federation.
I think that's about it.
All of that's true?
Okay, maybe I got a little
carried away, but remember,
it's for the sake of Imanity.
It definitely has nothing
to do with being in love.
( menacing voice )
Now then, dear Jibril,
tell me what you know about
the Eastern Federation,
the sexy animal‐girl paradise
we're about to conquer.
Well, I guess this country's
pretty much done for.
As you wish, my King.
Jibril:
The various Warbeast clans
were embroiled in the civil war
for many years,
mostly due
to physical differences,
but the shrine priestess
put an end to the battles
in less than half a century.
The clans unified
into a massive naval empire
and became the world's
third‐largest country,
the Eastern Federation.
Sora:
So, a land of cat girls,
dog girls, fox girls,
rabbit girls, and all other
kinds of animal girls,
and they'll all be mine.
All right,
we must conquer them at once.
( normal voice )
But to do that,
we'll need to utilize
all that precious knowledge
you've been collecting
over the last millennia.
I am sorry, master,
I doubt that would do much good.
Unfortunately, I can think
of no path to victory
when it comes to facing
the Eastern Federation.
Jibril,
you don't mean that.
You're saying
Blank can't win?
Not quite.
What I mean is
I won't be of much help
in forming
your strategy.
There was once
a time where I, too,
fought the Eastern
Federation... and lost.
( all gasp )
Kurami:
That settles it.
I knew Elkia
had another nation's support.
It must be the Warbeasts.
Okay, then, so what
you think is going on?
You of all
people should know.
Kurami:
On at least four occasions,
Elven Gard challenged
the Eastern Federation,
and lost each time.
Fiel:
Hmm... we might have won
if the players weren't
those senile elders,
but okay.
The point is,
when I faced Blank, I lost,
and that means they were able
to overcome your Elven magic,
and that Flugel was next.
In other words,
they must be using
some sort of
Warbeast sorcery
that even an Elf
couldn't detect.
Are you sure?
That's gotta
be it.
There's no way
Imanity could beat
a higher race
by itself.
Sora:
Don't underestimate humanity.
He's got some nerve.
( sighs )
So you and the Elves both got
your asses handed to you?
What the hell kind of game
did you play anyway?
When setting the rules,
one of the Federation's
conditions is that the loser
has their memories
of the game erased.
Now do you understand
what I mean?
Yeah, I get it,
it's impossible.
What you mean
it's impossible?
Sora: If they wipe your memories
when you lose
and you have no recollection
of the game,
how are you gonna adapt
your strategy
the next time
you challenge them?
To top it off, they can also
read your mind?
How are we supposed to beat
a race like that?
Shiro:
Don't be such a Steph, Steph.
It's pretty obvious.
( growls )
Huh? No, wait a second.
It doesn't add up.
What doesn't?
Since trying to beat
the Warbeasts is so pointless,
their enemies should eventually
stop trying, right?
It would be less painful
that way for everyone.
That, dear sis, is why
you suck at strategy games
despite being
a little smarter than me.
They've got some kind
of slam‐dunk method
of beating Flugel
and even Elves.
Why don't they pretend
like they're vulnerable instead?
Then they'd lure the enemy in,
give them a healthy beat down,
and snatch their land easy.
That play style
is just... mean.
Appalled!
Shiro:
There is something
weird about it, though.
How could they have expanded
their country so much
in just half a century?
Sora:
See? I told you
it's strange!
Master, wait,
I just thought of something.
I think I might be able
to explain how that happened.
Oh, really now?
Let's hear it.
I saw something
in here somewhere.
Only one country has challenged
the Eastern Federation
in the last ten years.
Only one?
Who's dumb enough to do that?
Why don't I just show you?
It'll be faster.
Come along, Dolly,
you're going with us.
All right then, masters.
Hold on tight
and don't let go.
Now then,
if everyone is ready.
( screams )
( surprised grunting )
Wha‐what's going on?!
Wow, it's so nice
and clear today.
J‐Jibril, what the heck
did you just do?!
Ever hear of teleporting?
Right, I keep forgetting.
I'm living
in a fantasy world now.
So how far can
you teleport?
I can travel as far
as I can see
and to any location
I've visited before.
Both:
So a zoom spell.
How was poor little Imanity
able to survive in a war
against a whole race
full of monsters like her?
That's been the most perplexing
mystery in all our history.
Oh, I remember it like
it was just yesterday.
The Dragonia, Giganto,
and Old Deus
all storming the battlefield,
50 Flugel desperately fighting
to sever a single
Dragon's head,
and then 200 of our finest
facing a god in vain!
Why, I can almost smell
the blood.
( all groan )
Ah, yes,
the good old days.
Have a look over
there, master.
Sora:
What I'm looking at here?
Some ugly high‐rise crapping up
the fantasy landscape?
Shiro:
It's huge.
Steph:
Oh, that's the Eastern
Federation's Elkian embassy.
Well, that kind of seems
like overkill, do you think?
Actually, that used to be
the Elkian palace,
but the Eastern Federation
did a bit of remodeling.
Ah! Hey,
hold on!
So that place
used to be your palace?
Why do they have it?
All starting
to make sense now, Master?
In the last ten years,
only one country
has challenged the Federation.
Uh‐huh, and
blew it, too.
Yeah. The
challenger was Elkia.
Shiro:
You hanging in there, Sora?
Sora:
Yeah, sorry, just wallowing
in despair, that's all.
UWAH!
Sora:
Even the Elves gave up
after four losses,
but Elkia challenged
these guys eight times
and bet half its kingdom?
I'm starting to think that
old King really was an idiot.
Hey, what was that?
Weren't you the one
that kept claiming
that he was right despite
what everyone else said?
Sora:
And thanks to his recklessness,
your territory got cut in half.
You expect me to defend that?
Can you just imagine
all the industry and farming
we could have if the country
still had all that land?
Man, he was as hopeless
as you are.
Did he just suck
at getting lucky
thinking if he kept
trying that eventually
he might somehow win?
Okay, maybe it's true
that my grandfather
wasn't good at games,
but he wasn't stupid enough
to risk the three million lives
under his care unless
he had a good reason.
The people came first!
Unlike the two of you,
he was kind and loving
and reasonable at least.
Well, excuse me
for being cruel and awful.
Heh. Besides, if throwing
away half your shit
qualifies you as reasonable,
that I'm happier being a jerk.
Eh, Maybe you're right
and he was a good king,
But just a good king
for a bunch of whiners
that won't take things
into their own hands.
That's more likely.
Useless friggin' humans,
completely hopeless,
every last one of them.
Huh?
You can go ahead and mock me,
I don't care.
But don't insult my grandfather
or what he believed in.
Hey, Steph,
wait, come back!
Too far, way too far.
After finding out about this
ridiculous state of affairs,
how else should I react?
Hmm?
They're yummy.
( impressed ) Damn.
They are good.
Steph:
Um, Granddaddy,
what's this key for?
Well, sweetie,
it opens the lock to something
I've stored away
that's very important.
Oooh! I've heard
about that!
So it's for
your secret man books
that you can't show
to other people?
No, no, my dear,
that's something else.
( stammers ) This key,
this is a key of hope.
Hope, huh?
Maybe someday,
it will belong to you.
What do I do with it,
Granddaddy?
Grandfather:
I want you to find someone
very special to give it to,
someone to whom
you can entrust our kingdom,
someone who can carry
the weight of Imanity's future.
Like hell I'm ever giving this
to that stupid‐
Hey, there, you got a second?
( screams )
What the heck
are you doing here?!
Dolly, I highly recommend
you return
to the library immediately.
What's going on now?
Though I came here
on my own,
I feel your presence
would benefit my Master.
Jibril:
However, I won't force you.
Huh?
This is so ridiculous.
Like they even care about me.
( groans softly )
Fine! I'll go!
Jibril:
Master, no matter
how hard you look, I doubt
you'll find evidence to justify
the King's foolish actions.
No, that's not
what I'm looking for.
Something about this
is bugging me, though.
You wouldn't happen to be
looking for clues
to help Dolly feel better,
now would you?
Look, I'm just reviewing
all the info so I don't make
the same mistake on my
animal‐girl‐kingdom conquest.
So anyway,
why'd the former king
challenge the
Federation eight times?
Sora:
A reasonable man responsible
for three million people
wouldn't just rush
into defeat again and again.
Right here, isn't this the first
place he offered up as a wager?
That's an omatite mine,
isn't it?
Sora:
Even though it's
a valuable metal,
Imanity doesn't have
the technology to refine it,
so it's worthless to us.
Then here's the second bet,
then the third bet,
the fourth bet, and
finally the eighth, here.
Up till the very last game
when he bet the castle,
looks like he didn't wager
anything of value.
Come on, I know we had
a reason for it, but why?
Master?
Why wipe challengers' memories
when it only discourages them?
Why did Elven Gard
challenge them four times?
Why did the former king‐
no, wait.
Maybe he stopped at eight
'cause maybe by the eighth time,
he actually achieved his goal.
There is no written proof,
but what if the last King
didn't lose his memories
after all?
Master, please don't take
this as being rude,
but from what I've seen,
not all Imanity act
with the same forethought
and attention as you.
Not all, but I'm sure
some of them do,
and most of the time,
they're probably misunderstood.
Now is the new King, it's my
duty to try and understand them.
I know what you're thinking‐
how can I possibly believe
that an inferior race like
humanity actually has a chance?
No, I wasn't thinking
that at all.
The answer's
simple, really.
If you want to know the truth,
I don't believe in humanity.
Humans are lowly
and stupid creatures,
every single last one of them,
including me.
They're all crap.
It doesn't matter
what planet they're from,
this one or my old one.
Not a damn thing's
changed a bit.
I...
I've heard enough.
However, I believe
in humanity's potential.
( gasps )
If you need proof,
it's right here.
This little human
is the real deal.
She's a shining example
of our potential,
our strength,
our hope, and our dreams
that reach even
beyond the gods.
I remember the
first day we met.
It was almost
eight years ago.
Back then,
she was only three.
The first time
she heard my name,
guess what her response was.
You seem so empty.
Sora:
First off, she knew
that my name meant sky,
and then she noticed
that I was smiling
just 'cause everyone else
in the room was.
A double entendre
at three years old.
I was so pumped.
This was it.
I found someone
who was worth something.
Also... ( sighs )
I wanted to be like her
or at least try.
You know,
back in our old world,
humans can fly through the sky
and even travel
amongst the stars.
Jibril:
Sorry, but that's
kind of hard to believe.
Sora:
Yeah, no kidding,
even humanity itself doubted
any of that was possible,
but someone
eventually pulled it off,
the real deal, pulled it off.
That's why it's up to us
to ensure that the potential
of the misunderstood
gets realized
before it all goes to waste.
And that's the reason why I need
to start believing in him.
The former king was right.
Sora...
Huh?
I have something that I...
want to give you.
There's no doubt.
It's his porn.
I knew it!
But my dear Master, which door
do you think it goes to?
People usually stash
their porn in their own room.
So then,
it's this one.
Actually, sis and I
found it a long time ago.
Peace.
Huh?
Sora:
Remember when I said
this bed was lopsided
and hard to sleep on?
That was just the start
of the puzzle.
With a little messing around
here and there...
Ah, there you go, one secret
room coming right up.
I give up.
I don't know anything.
( gasps ) Hmm.
( all gasp )
Grandfather:
I leave this in hopes
that you will not be
Imanity's last king
but rather
the one who restores it.
I admit,
I am not a wise king.
In fact, I fully expect
to be remembered
as one of the most foolish.
But that is of no matter.
I take up this pen
for the future King,
the one who will one day
bring us to glory.
All I can do is trust that
the story of my pathetic
and seemingly
hopeless struggles...
Steph: ( overlapping )
Will someday assist you
in your quest
as our next king.
Sora:
I knew it.
The old king didn't have
his memories erased after all.
Unlike the Elves,
the Warbeasts knew
Imanity didn't stand
a chance to win
and looked down on them
as easy prey.
They didn't erase his memories
because they wanted him
to keep trying.
Shiro:
Was that some way
to lure him in?
Sora:
They purposefully
went easy on him
to make him think he could
beat them the next time.
But still, the king knew that,
and he challenged them anyway
hoping to figure out
how their game worked.
He deliberately gave them
useless land
that he'd eventually
try to take back.
So then if he played
so many times,
why didn't he reveal the secrets
of the game to anyone?
They probably made him
take a pledge,
like he couldn't tell people
as long as he lived.
So it was all
for nothing?
Not quite.
Once he died, the pledge
no longer applied.
Sora:
He bet eight times,
but then he found a loophole
in the pledges,
then entrusted that information
to the next king.
Humanity's greatest gambler.
Shiro:
That's why he set up
a gambling tournament
to find the next ruler,
even if it ousted Steph.
Sora:
Your former King,
he made a bet.
He bet that a human,
someone from
the lowest‐ranked race,
would rise up and crush
all the other races.
Grandfather:
The possibility rests
ever so close to naught.
However...
it still remains.
Sora:
Steph...
He just pretended
to be a fool,
lost the bets
but kept trying.
In reality,
he was a great man
trying to save Imanity
up until his death.
This is his trust
in our people.
You know what, Steph?
Your old Gramps‐
no, sorry,
I mean the former king...
( chuckles )
he really was
a great man after all.
Granddaddy!
( crying ) Granddaddy!
Well, it sure is one hell
of a task he threw at us.
Don't worry, Sora,
you and I can do it.
See, Jibril? Not all
humans are so bad.
What do you think?
You ready for this?
Jibril:
Yes, ready indeed, Master.
Sora and Shiro:
Eastern Federation,
your head's gonna look
mighty nice on the end
of this pike.