Queen:
I don't believe this!
There's only four of them!
They beat 1,200 players
all on their own?
( grunts )
Enough, this ends now!
( chuckles )
Queen:
You're mine.
( gasps )
Queen:
No! You can't
dodge that.
You can't dodge that!
Boy:
Tell me if this story
rings a bell.
It may just be an urban legend,
but I assure you,
it's a good one.
There exists a band
of anonymous players,
gamers who obliterate
anyone who comes to face them,
reaching scores never
achieved before or since.
In every game they play,
their win records are flawless.
Since their user names
are always left empty,
they are simply known
to people as "Blank."
And according to every player
who has encountered them,
they're indeed unbeatable.
Cheaters?
You think that's how
they keep winning?
Yeah. I'm sure of it.
It's got to be just
a lousy group of hackers.
Come on, there's no way
they could beat 1,200 people
with just the four of them.
Auto‐aimers and wall hacks,
hitbox manipulation.
They got to be cheating.
Oh, do they?
And here I thought cheating
was our expertise.
Otherwise,
I'd wouldn't be able
to cast so many spells
like that.
Man:
I don't know.
This is different.
Queen:
But Blank dodged them anyway.
They already knew
I was cheating
to cast consecutive spells
before I even did it.
They're amazing.
They're like super geniuses
or something!
You think maybe
they'd go out with me?!
Man:
Oh, God.
Queen:
( cackling )
Boy:
And so the rumors spread with
their infamy.
You know, urban legends
are like a kind of wish.
Because...
( powers down )
in reality...
the least interesting answer
is usually the correct one.
( sighs )
We won... somehow.
Hey, listen, Little Sis,
could you do me a favor
and please stop controlling
the main account for Blank
with your feet?
Kind of nasty.
Hungry, I'm still hungry.
Want some, Sora?
Sora:
Sure, why not?
( electronic music plays )
Sora:
Really splurging on some
fancy rations, huh, Shiro?
Shiro:
Nutrition's important.
Listen, the human brain
can function
as long as it has glucose.
White bread is best
in terms of cost‐performance.
Yeah.
Thanks for the lecture.
But I need other types
of nutrients, too,
or I won't get any bigger.
Sora:
You're already a perfect,
flawless beauty,
you darling girl.
Mm.
Sora:
Hey, what time is it?
Shiro:
Um... 8:00 A. M.,
the middle of the night.
Sora: What day?
Does that even
matter to a NEET?
It does!
It tells me when MMORPGs
are going to have new events!
And wha‐ wait!
I know you've been up
for five days straight,
but if you quit now,
I won't have a healer!
I know you can do it.
You seriously think
I can control four characters
at one time?
Shiro:
Just believe.
Wait, no!
Please don't fall asleep!
If you go to sleep,
Shiro, everyone‐
and by everyone,
I mean me‐ will die!
( shouts )
Okay, fine, fine,
I'll do it!
I can take these suckers!
( mouse clicking rapidly )
(birds chirping)
Boy:
This world is chaotic,
unfair, and unforgiving.
It has no meaning or value.
However, some people simply
refuse to accept this,
even though they know
they can't change anything.
They wish that
the world could be
just a little more interesting.
And that's how
urban legends are formed,
from wishes like that.
Okay, so let's get
things started.
Let's offer a subtle
stylistic catalyst
for a chance
at a new beginning.
Let's ask the question...
"Have you ever heard
the latest rumor?"
(tablet beeps)
Email.
Sora:
Listen, your brother's been
playing four characters
Sora:
Listen, your brother's been
playing four characters
on four separate screens.
I don't know what you want,
but I'm seriously about
to drop dead here.
Shiro:
It may be from a friend.
Whose friend?
Shiro:
Your friend?
( wheezes and laughs)
That's weird.
I thought I heard my sister
say something really mean
and sarcastic to me.
Huh?
Sora:
What is this?
And how does this guy know that
the two of us are siblings?
What should we do?
Sora:
Is he trying to
cut a deal with us?
Well, it might be fun
to see where this goes.
Huh? Chess?
Shiro:
Well, good night.
( thud )
Huh, wait, wait!
Don't fall asleep yet.
I can't handle a high‐level
chess simulation on my own!
Sora:
Chess is a finite
two‐player, zero‐sum,
perfect information game.
Luck plays no part in it.
Theoretically, to each game,
there is a perfect solution
that will never fail.
Of course, that's only
if you have a mind capable
of calculating
the 10'^120 possible states
of the board.
Shiro:
Chess is no different
than simply playing
tic‐tac‐toe.
That's right.
Sora:
Shiro has beaten
a program designed
to defeat grandmasters
20 times in a row,
alternating between
going first and second.
However...
( gasps )
Shiro:
It cut off
its own piece's advance.
Hold on, Shiro.
What?
A program will always
select the best strategy.
You can win 'cause
they're predictable.
But this one's deliberately
using a bad move
to lure you in.
Sora:
It's a human.
Shiro:
Hmm...
Don't worry, if it's
a contest of skill,
you've got this
in the bag.
Sora:
I'll tell you when they're up
to something tricky.
The two of us,
Sora and Shiro,
form two halves of a whole.
Now let's see
if there's somebody
who's got the balls
to beat us.
( both groan )
Male computerized voice:
Checkmate! You are winner!
( both sigh )
( yawning )
Yeah, we won!
I haven't worked
this hard in a long time.
Was that guy really human?
( chimes )
Together:
Huh?
What the hell?
Sora:
What do you mean,
"is it fun?"
In this game there's no way
to know the rules
or how to win,
yet there are 7 billion players
all making whatever
moves they want.
If you lose too much,
or win too much,
there are penalties.
You can't pass your turn,
and if you complain,
people look down on you.
There's no parameters
or freakin' genre
or anything.
You know what you call that?
You call it...
Sora and Shiro:
A crappy game.
( chimes )
( laughs )
Sora:
Uh, believe me,
if there's a world like that,
then the two of us,
well, we were born
in the wrong one, for sure.
( both gasp )
(static buzzing)
Huh? What the‐
Sora?
Boy:
You know what?
I think so, too!
In fact,
it sounds like you two
don't have any business living
in this world at all!
( both shout )
Boy:
So how does this sound?
How would you like
a second chance to be made anew
in the world in which
you should have been born
in the first place?
Welcome to the world
of my creation!
( both shout )
What's going on?!
( shouts )
This is the ideal world
you've always dreamed of‐
the world of games!
It's Disboard!
Sora:
Shit!
You see, everything
in this world
(whimper)
is decided by a simple game‐
Government, politics,
even the lives of its people.
Shiro:
Who are you?
Me?
They call me Tet.
I live over here.
I'm a god.
A god?
You're so short.
Now's not the time!
We're gonna die!
Try to stay focused, please.
So everything here is decided
by ten simple pledges.
( beep )
One‐ Killing others,
waging war,
and stealing from people
is strictly forbidden
in this world.
(beep)
Tet:
Two‐ All conflicts,
no matter how great or small,
must be resolved
through games.
(beep)
Three‐
Before the games begin,
each player
must bet something
that they agree
is of equal value.
( beep )
Four‐ As long as it doesn't
go against number three,
what they bet
and the rules of the game
will not be questioned.
( beep )
Five‐ The challenged party has
the right to determine
the rules of the game.
( beep )
Six‐ All bets made in
accordance with the pledges
must be upheld.
(beep)
Seven‐ Conflicts between
groups will be overseen
by appointed representatives
with absolute authority.
( beep )
Eight‐ Being caught cheating
during a game
results in an instant loss.
(beep)
And nine‐ In the name
of Almighty God,‐that's me‐
the previous rules
may never be altered.
Okay, great, now would you
shut up and save us?!
Sora:
The ground! the ground,
the ground, the ground!
Shiro!
Sora!
(explosion)
Sora:
( grunts )
( wheezes )
Number ten‐
Let's all have fun
and play together!
( laughs )
Sora:
Huh? Hey!
Tet:
( distantly ) I look forward
to seeing you two again.
I'm pretty sure
it won't be long.
Sora?
Shiro:
Where are we?
( wind whistles )
(loud crash)
( roars )
You know what, sis?
Hmm?
Sora:
I've always thought life
was just a game
for masochists and losers,
and what happened?
The game just crashed!
Oh, what's going on?
Together:
This game is total crap!
Man:
Long ago, in the
far distant past,
the gods, along with
their families and creations,
waged a seemingly
never‐ending war
for the right
to rule this world,
They fought for the right
to become the One True God.
Eventually, it became clear
there would be no real victor,
as the sky, the sea,
the land and the stars
were all destroyed
in the devastating battles.
However,
hidden amongst the wreckage,
a single deity
had survived.
Although he never participated
in the conflict,
the title became his.
His name was Tet,
and he was known
as the God of Play.
Tet:
You creatures who have
fought with violence,
blood, and death,
who built a tower of corpses
that rises to the sky,
and who still
call yourselves wise,
tell me this:
What makes you different
from wild animals?
Man:
In the face
of their shattered world,
excuses were meaningless
and God spoke‐
"Thou shalt not kill
one another.
Murder and thievery
in this realm
is henceforth forbidden."
Tet:
You 16 races full
of greed and hubris,
I command you to use
your ingenuity and wit,
your great fortunes
and power
to build me a tower
of knowledge
and to prove to me...
Man:
Your strength of mind.
Okay, I think I get it.
So everything in this world
is decided by games,
because the God of Play
is in charge?
That's right,
and by the way...
Hmm? What now?
Do you suppose
you could find it in your heart
to at least leave us
a pair of pants?
Sora:
Uh, Numero seis‐ Any bets made
in accordance with the pledges
must be upheld.
So we bet everything
we could offer,
including our lives,
and you in turn,
bet everything
you had on you,
which just so happened
to include your pants.
Okay, that's true,
but still,
You can't leave us here
like this!
Let's go, Shiro.
(all screaming)
Roger.
Please, double or nothing!
I can't go back to
the village in my undies.
Sora:
Huh, seems like even bandits
can't rob or kill you.
That's pretty convenient.
Nah, I bet they couldn't
even if they tried.
Anyway.
Seems like everything comes down
to your skill at the game.
( grunting )
Hey, how about you
speed this up?
Would you shut up!
I'm thinking here!
I just need a second,
okay?
Yeah, you can think
all you want,
but it won't change
your hand.
Sora:
A gambling tournament to decide
the next king?
It was the Old King's
dying wish.
Apparently,
he wanted the next ruler
to be humanity's
greatest gambler or something.
Huh, so even the ruler
is decided by a game.
Woman:
The red‐headed girl is
Stephanie Dola.
She's the granddaughter
of the Former King,
but because of his will,
she can't inherit the throne.
So she's entered the gambling
tournament as well.
Hmm? Hey, Shiro,
are you doing okay?
Shiro:
I'm good.
Huh?
What's the matter?
Got a crush?
Yeah, right.
I was just wondering if you
were going to enter this thing.
Who, me?
Oh, no, this is all I need
right here, Kiddo.
And... besides...
Kurami over there
is so strong that most
of the other players
have already pulled out
before they had
the chance to lose.
In other words,
you're too scared to enter?
What'd you say?
So, as long as you
don't actually lose to her,
you can go home and tell
all your friends
whatever you want,
am I right?
"Oh, I won because
she was so pathetic.
I let her go."
Well, aren't you something?
So let's play,
Little Boy.
Sorry, but I don't play
for fun.
You got to put something
on the line...
like that bag of cash.
What? Do you know much
is in here?
The deal is that
we have to bet something
of equal value
or it isn't official.
Pledge three, right?
I suppose that's fair.
How's this?
You can do whatever
you want with the two of us.
Our lives are yours.
Sora:
Sell us, leave us to die,
your choice.
Seriously?
Why not?
Sora:
We'll play a single hand
of poker.
Uh...
What do you say?
I'd love to show one
of the locals how it's done.
Confident, huh?
Better watch that mouth
of yours.
All right,
have it your way.
I swear by the pledges.
Together: Aschente!
Woman:
Just a stupid redneck kid
with more confidence
than experience.
A bluff like that might work
on the backward dolts
in your village...
...but not here!
Sora.
Oh, no, run into
some bad luck?
Poor baby.
Yeah, I started the day
with a 10,000‐meter skydive,
then walked forever
under the blazing sun.
through some screwed‐up
wilderness‐
definitely a bad day.
You did what now?
Just forget I said anything.
You ready?
( chuckles )
Ready... and waiting.
How about you?
Perhaps you'd like
to draw the cards again?
No thanks, we're cool.
Oh.
In that case...
too bad, kiddo!
Full house, Asshole!
Oh, you're right.
That is too bad.
Huh?
( gasps )
Ro...
Royal...
s‐straight...
f‐f‐flush?!
( wails )
Oh, no way!
No friggin' way
( shrieks )
Uh, yeah, way.
That's more than one
in 6 million odds!
Yep, and you just got
really unlucky.
But how?!
Sora:
Pledge six‐
All bets must be upheld,
am I right?
So pay up.
Just... who are you people?
Nobody special, just...
a new player in town.
Sora, that was mean.
You could have least tried
to hide you were cheating.
Well, let's review pledge
number eight, shall we?
Being caught cheating during
a game means an instant loss.
In other words,
if you're not caught, it's fine.
How much is in there?
No clue.
Well, just leave it to me.
Big Bro's an expert
at negotiations.
I'll take a room.
One bed will be just fine.
How many nights
would this get me?
Just one night.
( chuckles )
I'm really tired.
Come on, dude,
You're gonna tell me
how many nights
I can really stay here?
If you're trying
to cheat someone,
you should pay
more attention to your tone
and where you're looking at.
Fine, two nights, then.
Man, you really
are not good at this!
Listen, Pierre,
if you're gonna lie,
you better be careful
who you do it to, okay?
Man: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, four nights,
awesome.
Hey, kid,
what's your name?
Hmm?
You can just leave it blank.
Sorry for the wait,
Shiro.
That girl's
about to lose it.
Sora:
No kidding.
Doesn't look like anyone taught
her what "poker face" means,
unlike her opponent.
Hmm, she's cheating.
Think so, yeah.
But how?
It doesn't make sense.
Now wait a minute.
Something else
is going on here.
( laughs )
Seriously?
Kurami:
You can fold
whenever you want.
Stephanie:
Would you please
shut up already!
Just be quiet and focus
on your own cards, all right?
Finally!
Listen,
that girl is cheating.
Uh...
Hey, you still playing
or what?
Huh? Oh, yes,
of course I am.
Sora:
Smartphones, DSPs, Tablet PC.
I got the battery
and the solar charger,
cables, and everything.
Well, all things considered,
Is this it?
after everything
that happened today,
I'd say we're lucky
to have this much.
I can't connect.
Figures.
This really is an
honest‐to‐God fantasy world.
And the way
she was cheating...
that was like
its own fantasy, too.
Sora, can you beat
real magic?
I guess that
was a dumb question.
Hey, Shiro...
usually, in, like,
comics and stuff
when the main characters
end up in another world,
they try their best
to find a way home, right?
Sora:
But why would they want
to go back to a world
if it's total... shit?
( sighs softly )
( chuckles )
Shiro:
I thought the same thing.
Well, then it's settled.
Sora:
Let the real game begin.
( theme song plays )
( taps on door )
Shiro, as your brother,
I'm really happy
that you love me so much,
but let go of me for a second.
( footsteps )
Sora:
Who's there?
Come on, man,
I paid up front already.
Would it be okay
if I came in for a second?
Shiro:
We're gonna save the day?
Sora:
Sure, why not,
it'll be fun, right?