That's kind of
ridiculously overdone.
Jibril:
Why would they ever need
to build something
so absurdly huge?
They couldn't possibly
be trying to compensate
for something,
could they?
Okay, well, this was
a nice little vacation
but could you please take me
far away from this place now?
Hey, wait, this embassy's
on foreign soil.
Sora:
Yeah, yeah, but it was
originally our castle,
too, you know.
Steph:
But this is an invasion
of their territory.
Just relax, I made
an appointment already.
Hey there!
Greetings, Lord Sora
and Lady Shiro.
Welcome to our embassy.
I'm the assistant ambassador
to the Elkian embassy,
Ino Hatsuse.
A pleasure to meet you.
Wait, when did‐
This morning.
I could see the old dude
checking me out in the library,
so I signaled to him
I'd come over.
Man, just like they say,
those Warbeast senses
really are awesome.
It's like they've got
telescopic vision.
You could've told me
about this, you know.
Undoubtedly the reason
for your visit is to meet
with Ambassador Izuna Hatsuse.
Is that correct?
Steph:
It looks like the
rumors really were true.
The Warbeasts can
read people's minds.
Glad to hear we're all
on the same page.
Right, let's get moving.
Very well.
This way, if you please.
Steph:
Forget about the Warbeasts.
How did Sora see him
from way over there?
Sora:
In case you hadn't noticed...
Uh...
The game...
it's already begun,
hasn't it?
Sora:
Hey, Jibril?
Jibril:
Yes?
Sora:
What do you guys
call this?
Jibril:
It's an image
display device.
But wait, the Warbeasts
can't use magic,
so I don't know
how they're doing it.
My, but it is rather
fascinating! (giggles)
Cool.
( screams ) What's going on?
Why have the floor moving?
Pardon, but I beg you
follow proper procedures
when making an
appointment next time.
Due to an incident,
many Warbeasts
harbor extreme animosity
toward Elkia.
Since you arrived so quickly,
most weren't informed
and may not act
entirely... civil.
Well, that makes sense,
I mean, a dog
that talks and walks
is still just a dog, right?
Hey, Steph, what incident?
Yeah, he's referring
to the Construction Wars.
Having a foreign embassy
bigger than our palace
was really bad for our image,
so we ended up building
a new bigger one.
Sora:
That's the one
we live in now, right?
Steph:
No, 'cause after that,
the Eastern Federation built
their embassy even bigger,
so we had to keep competing.
But when it comes
to construction technology,
Elkia lags way behind
the Eastern Federation, so‐
Isn't that ironic?
If I recall, the Warbeasts
are only ranked 14 themselves,
so looking down
on Imanity is... well,
I'm not sure how
your people say it,
but we say it's like a moron
laughing at an imbecile.
( laughs )
That may be true in a sense,
but it seems a bit petty
coming from someone
from the sixth order.
Speaking of which, as a weapon,
I fear you're defective
if you're serving
a bunch of shaved monkeys.
Sora:
Okay, guess relations in this
world are pretty strained, huh?
Steph:
The war dragged on forever,
and thanks to the ten pledges,
they can't get violent,
so they ended up letting out
their aggression
this way instead.
(elevator dings)
( laughter and groaning )
Ino:
( clears throat )
My lords, please wait here.
Steph:
Each culture certainly
has its own style, huh?
Master,
you never told us
how you make contact
with the Warbeasts.
Nobody's talking about it,
so just take the hint, okay?
I apologize for
prying, master.
But I can't read minds
like the beasts here
and I really,
really want to know.
Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell
me, tell me, tell me, tell me.
Both: Hmm?
Jibril:
So even with your
little magic rectangle,
you still couldn't
see him clearly,
but you guessed
that he saw you
and gestured to him
accordingly, is that right?
Steph:
Don't tell me you bluffed
someone who can read minds.
Ino:
I apologize for the wait.
Presenting the
Eastern Federation's
ambassador to Elkia,
Miss Izuna Hatsuse.
Sora and Shiro:
Erase time!
Pretty girl with animal ears,
want to come play with me?
I'm a little bit of a perv,
but I've got a clean record.
( panting laugh )
Why the hell are you assholes
touching me, please?
( stammers )
What?!
Minus 50 cuteness points
for sure.
Who said you shitheads
could stop? Thank you.
You popped out of nowhere
and surprised me is all, please.
Commence the petting,
peasants, thank you.
Both:
Uh...
Adding "please" and "thank you"
at the end of a sentence
doesn't automatically
make it polite, you know.
Of course it does,
you idiot, thanks.
I apologize
if she has offended you.
My granddaughter's still getting
a grasp of the Imanity language.
Oh, and by the way...
KEEP YOUR FILTHY MONKEY PAWS
OFF OF HER,
you hairless primates,
or I'll rip you a new asshole!
Or that's what I would say
if you weren't so charming.
So I guess she gets it
from the old fart, huh?
He's a bad accessory.
Minus 1,000 points.
But I just love her
conflicting personalities.
Plus 1,050 points.
You hairless monkeys do that
way better than grandpa.
( roars )
Please, keep going. Thank you.
Look, why don't we give
the whole monkeys thing a rest?
I'm Sora. That's my
little sister Shiro.
Nice to meet
you, Izuna.
Sora and Shiro, got it.
Please, thanks.
Ino:
Well, then, let us hear
what you feces‐tossing apes
have to say.
Sora:
I thought you could
read our minds.
Ino:
This is a place of diplomacy,
a place to exchange ideas.
Or is that too complicated for
you knuckle‐dragging gorillas?
Sora:
Don't get pissed.
She just likes us better, Pops.
He's so immature.
Master, I advise you
to be careful not to shatter
the Warbeast's fragile,
dainty heart.
He's so pathetic,
we wouldn't want
to hurt his little feelings.
( screams )
Didn't anyone teach
you people manners?
All right, gramps, I'll tell you
what we're here for.
How about we play a game,
and you bet your
granddaughter's panties?
And I'll put up
Steph's for my bet.
Hmm?
IF YOU WANTED ME TO ROLL YOU
IN A RUG AND BEAT TO DEATH,
You Should Have Just Said So,
You Damned Monkey!
What? You'd rather have
Jibril's than Steph's?
Certainly, as you wish,
my master.
Sora:
Don't tell me
you want Shiro's.
Come on, gramps, that's sick.
She's only 11 years old.
No, don't tell me.
You don't want mine, do you?
Sorry, but I don't
swing that way.
Shiro:
It's okay, Sora,
I'll protect your chastity.
Sora:
Too many choices or what?
Her panties are a pretty
good deal for you, old‐timer.
Please excuse me,
but if you refuse to tell us
why you're really here,
then maybe it's best‐
Drop the pathetic act already.
Hmm?
If you can read thoughts
like you say,
then I'd suggest you go
for the panty game.
Look, I know it's not
the panties you're after.
It's just a low stakes match,
and a good chance
to wipe away all my memories
about your games.
So let's shake on it.
Oh, second‐guessing, huh?
Looks like I was right.
Smells to me like cold reading,
cheap parlor tricks
that don't even need the
amazing senses of a Warbeast,
just some observational skills
and a bit of intuition.
Coincidently,
that just so happens
to be a specialty of mine.
Ino: Is he...
So you done confirming
this isn't a bluff yet?
( chuckles )
Now then,
since we've established
that your so‐called
mind‐reading ability
is a bunch of crap,
let's get down to business.
Like why we really
paid you a visit.
We, Sora and Shiro,
designated representatives
of the 16th order of Imanity
in the kingdom of Elkia...
Shiro:
Have blessed the
Eastern Federation
with the opportunity to become
the first honorable sacrifice
on our path
to world domination.
Therefore, we hereby
challenge you
to a game between nations.
Both:
And we demand everything
the Eastern Federation
has on this continent.
Steph:
A game between nations?
So you mean we're
officially attacking
the Eastern Federation?
Did I really just
hear you correctly?
Yep, and by the way,
we're not changing our bet.
It's still for Steph's panties.
(screams)
Should have just bet
Izuna's panties while
you had the chance.
Sorry, Gramps,
them's the breaks.
And that's a check.
Master, could you please explain
the madness going on here?
What's wrong, Jibril?
You still don't understand?
Basically, we've got the
Federation backed into a corner.
Sora:
Over the last 50 years,
their technology evolved
pretty rapidly,
and they grew more
and more powerful,
but despite being so advanced,
they're still an island nation
that needs resources
from the mainland.
Before they could even set foot
on the main continent,
Elven Gard attacked,
or perhaps they were lured in.
Either way, no other country
would agree to play
an unknown game that even the
strongest nation kept losing.
The Federation couldn't
get onto the continent.
They should have just lost
so more countries
would challenge them,
but for some reason,
they didn't.
Let's solve these mysteries
in order, shall we?
Question one!
Why do they wipe all
memories of the game?
If they don't, they won't
be able to win every time.
Correct! It defeats the goal
of luring others into play.
Even though
it's not entirely logical,
they wipe memories
because there's something
they're trying
to keep secret.
But still, you can erase
people's memories
but not the fact
that they lost.
Question two!
Why'd Elven Gard challenge
them four times?
They knew
that they might lose,
but they wanted to figure out
what the game was.
Unlike Elkia, Elven Gard
is a really big country.
They were prepared
to suffer some losses
to do their research.
Sora:
After their first loss,
they figured it must have been
a game where you
couldn't use magic.
An Elf would think
that was the most likely reason
they'd lose a game.
So they came up with
some kind of countermove
and challenged a second time
and lost again.
Then they played a third time.
I'm not sure how,
but they figured something out.
So they went back to using
their official cheats
they call magic and made their
fourth and final challenge,
and they lost again.
That's quite
an imagination you have.
Sora:
In any case,
I'm not too concerned
with the way
they lost.
What I want to know is why
they stopped after four games.
If you think all that's just
my imagination, that's cool.
I mean, you're old
and kind of grumpy. I get it.
I see two options.
The first‐ they realized
the game was impossible to win.
And then the Elves could've
exposed the cheating and won.
Or second, they learned
the tricks of the game
but could never figure out
why they kept losing.
So that's why the Elves
stopped challenging them.
But still.
Now that's odd.
So what do we have here?
You were able
to figure out the game,
but you have no idea
why you kept losing.
Starting to get good,
party people!
Time for question three!
What works equally well
on these very different races?
What game would be
a guaranteed win
made by technology only
the Federation would have?
And the answer is?!
They made a video game where
you can cheat all you want.
Both:
They made a video game?
What the hell is a video game?
I doubt that you'd know,
Steph, but, Jibril,
you challenged the Eastern
Federation once already,
so how come you'd never seen
that thing at the
entrance before?
Jibril:
Uh, well,
I guess that's because‐
Sora:
Because you'd forgotten it.
It's a memory
associated with the game.
Still, despite all that,
if a Flugel like Jibril
doesn't know anything
about them,
it's pretty safe to say
the Federation
is the only country
in the world with video games.
You erased the memories to keep
the games a secret because‐
guess what everyone‐
in a video game
where you're the game master,
you can keep cheating your
ass off till the cows come home.
And your opponent,
who's busy running in circles,
stays clueless.
Plus, if you don't even know
what cyberspace is,
then magic's pointless.
All that mind‐reading garbage
is just a cover story
so your opponents
won't look closer
and find out
you're cheating, right?
Hang on,
we're almost done here.
Sora:
So you can tell
when someone's lying,
but there's no way
you can read their mind.
And the final question is?
Golly!
How in the world were they able
to figure all this out?
The answer's on the house, pops.
Do you care to take a guess?
Ino:
Don't tell me
it was the former king.
We made him swear by the pledges
to tell no one,
but even he didn't realize
we couldn't read minds.
No, that's not
the problem here.
Sora:
Right, that's not
the real problem.
You made the former king
promise not to speak
about the games to anyone,
but since he did,
it proves you couldn't
read his mind. How?
'Cause he pledged to tell
no one so long as he lived.
That doesn't mean he couldn't
tell anyone after he died.
So now that we know all about
your devious game,
are you starting to get
a little worried, Old Man?
'Cause if you're not, Gramps,
we'd be happy
to go to the Elves
and tell them
all about your tactics,
and you'd be forced
to play them all over again,
and you'd lose.
At this point, it's in your best
interest to erase our memories.
But if you're prepared
to bet your territory
just for Steph's panties,
then I guess that means
my imagination
must be correct.
Damn it.
Ino and Sora:
Then that means...
Your only other option
is to claim my theory
is just a load of crap
and run away
from our challenge,
right, Old Man?
Both:
But you said
you could run away?
I'll make it worth your while.
I'll throw in all of Imanity.
Huh?
( Steph screams )
And Imanity's race piece!
( all gasp )
K‐Kurami?
Why is‐
Listen, Fiel.
Do you know of any games
in the past
where someone bet
a race piece?
Of... of course not, never.
If you bet your
race piece and lose,
then you also lose
all your rights as an Exceed.
That means...
That the ten pledges
no longer apply.
In other words,
we're no better than animals.
It's like a death sentence
for all of Imanity.
That son of a bitch!
Sora, are you insane?
I've bet our entire territory
and put the lives
of all Imanity on the line.
If you try to back out now,
that's like telling
the entire world
that my imagination was correct.
Bet you didn't see
that coming, did you,
Mr. Freakin' Mind Reader?
Check and mate.
Ino:
Are you sure you
want to do this?
Even if you're correct,
keep in mind
Elven Gard still lost
this game four times.
Plus you dare bet
your precious race piece?
Do you want your people
to go extinct?
Say, Old Fart,
remember when I flagged
you down from the library?
Maybe if you'd thought
about how we could do that,
you'd have realized that the two
of us are not from this world.
When it comes to video games,
you can use as many cheats
or assists
as your heart desires.
None of that will help you.
Blank will never lose
to anything like that.
Sora:
When we showed up here...
Shiro:
Did you really think
we would just roll over
like easy prey?
Now it's your turn to be
the hunted, Warbeast friend.
Who the hell do these two
think they are?
( chuckles )
Well, guess
you can't agree
to a game of this scale
on your own, right?
We can do this another day.
We're betting our race piece,
so all of Imanity
has the right to watch.
The four of us are ready,
and we're not gonna
let you squirm
out of this.
But wait‐
I don't really get
any of this, thanks.
But, Sora, and Shiro,
sounds like you buttwads
challenged me to
a fight, so thanks.
A fight? No way.
Izuna, let's play a game
next time, okay?
I won't lose to losers,
thank you.
Sorry to disappoint,
but you will.
Everyone knows,
Blank never loses a game.
Shiro:
See you soon,
Little Izuna.
Steph:
You idiots, what the hell
were you thinking?!
Do you realize what you've done?
And what if you lose?
What the heck
are you gonna do?
I don't know.
If we lose, we're pretty much
done for, so what else is there?
I know if we lose,
it's game over
for us and three million people,
but if we win,
we get the animal girls
and their land.
Not too shabby, eh?
Isn't it so
exciting, Shiro?!
It's so exciting.
What... What's
wrong with you two?
Sora:
Just relax, Steph.
It's just a game, right?
Steph:
I knew it.
It was stupid and naive of me
to entrust these people
with my
grandfather's hopes.
If it bothers you, Dolly,
then consider this‐
if the Masters win,
every Warbeast on the planet
will be stripped of their land
and also their rights
and possibly face death.
Who do you think should take
responsibility for that?
Jibril:
We rule each other
and kill each other
through games
instead of violence.
The losers are exploited,
enslaved, and killed.
That's the essence
of the ten pledges,
being daring enough
not just to risk your own life
but also the lives
of all your people
just for the tiniest opportunity
to defeat your enemy.
Those are the qualities
we need in a ruler.
Sora and Shiro:
Huh? Say what now?
Steph and Jibril:
What?
Don't tell me you guys haven't
figured it all out yet.
The way to win,
the way to beat this world.
Steph and Jibril:
The way to win
and beat this world?
Well, now I see why God
gets so bored of this place.
Poor Tet.
I feel sorry for him.
Sora:
Don't worry, guys,
we'll conquer the hell
out of this world as promised,
the whole damn thing.
We won't lose.
There's no point
in even planning
for that sort of outcome.
No chance of us losing,
you got me?
And that's checkmate.
Man:
Come out here, you stupid kids!
( indistinct conversations
and angry shouting )
Jibril:
My, how quickly their attitudes
have changed almost overnight.
Steph:
How do you think
you'd feel
if you were suddenly given
a death sentence?
I think it's actually
pretty strange
that they're acting
this calm.
Are you going to do anything
to quiet them down?
Shiro:
If they were that mad,
they could try
and take the throne
back from us.
Sora:
It's just a bunch of whining,
and I doubt any of them
have the guts to challenge us.
More importantly,
what's the hold‐up?
It's been a week already.
You mean why the Federation
hasn't picked
a date for the game yet?
With their whole country
at stake, I'm sure it
will take some time.
Yeah, I figured
as much.
I'll just wait for someone with
more of a backbone to show up.
All:
Uh, huh?
Sora:
Looks like they're
finally here.
Kept me waiting long enough.
Yeah, of course
I know what you guys want.
I'm ready when you are.
Shiro, listen up, 'kay?
You know
that I believe in you.
Yeah, I know.
I believe in you too, Sora.
Shiro, never forget
the two of us are always one.
( gasps )
The two of us
are bound by a promise.
Shiro, we're not the heroes
of some stupid kid's manga.
Shiro, we've always won the
game before it's even started.
Sora?
I'll get the last piece to beat
the Federation, okay, Sis?
Sora?
No! W‐wait!
Sora:
( echoing )
Let's get this game
started, shall we?
( moaning softly )
Sora?
Shiro, rise and shine.
What's the matter?
Hey, what's wrong, Shiro?
Sora? Where are you?
Come help, please!
You can't leave me here alone!
Shiro, who are
you talking to?
Who's this Sora guy?
Do you want me
to go find him for you?
No way.
No way!
Shiro, is everything okay?
Steph?
Where's Sora?
Where is he?
My brother?
Brother?
You have a brother?
And his name's...
what again?
Shiro:
I won't let go
of your hand, Sora.
It would feel like
my soul was leaving me.