Hey there, Izuna.
What now, please?
Sora:
When's the last time
you really had fun
playing a game, huh?
Izuna:
I won't lose to losers.
Sora:
Sorry to disappoint you.
Shiro:
Everyone knows
Blank never loses a game.
This is fun!
Thank you!
No way!
A double jump?!
You gotta be kidding!
Cheater!
( grunts )
Wh‐what did she do?
Kurami:
I've heard of this,
an ability only
a few Warbeasts possess
that make them able to overcome
all physical limits,
Blood Destruction.
I won't lose, thank you.
My, my, my.
( door closes )
This is BS!
Not even Mario can do that!
It must be a glitch.
( roars )
She's too unpredictable.
The little kid's
all over the place!
Sora:
So then this was her
real cheat all along.
Ino:
( laughs )
The difference between
their strength
is too great to overcome.
This battle is already over.
Sora:
Okay, I predicted that
things will get a little hairy,
but I really
didn't expect this.
I can't calculate
what to do.
I know, she's practically
defying physics.
So trying to use those equations
isn't gonna help us.
Sora...
In times like this,
you can leave it to me.
I'm still king when
it comes to bluffs.
Sora:
At this rate of speed,
she'll no doubt predict
that I'll dodge.
So she'll try to block
both sides.
And once she decides
that I won't dodge after all,
she'll fire one
straight down the middle.
( gasps )
Two shots?
Damn it. Did she plan
this from the start?
No.
Ino:
Sora and Shiro's
heartbeats have gone flat,
a perfect headshot.
There's no way
to disguise that.
You've got them, Izuna!
You've got them!
( panting, heartbeat pounding )
( heartbeat slowing )
I won.
I won, thanks!
Yes, I did it!
Thank you!
( gunshot )
Huh?
What the hell was that?
So‐Sora?
Did I do it?
Did I get her?
Is it okay if I open my eyes
now, you guys?
Steph:
Shiro? Hey, are you
guys still there?
Answer me!
Well, looks
like it worked.
Sure does.
That's bullshit!
They couldn't have planned
all of that!
Even if you do have
a sixth sense,
bet you didn't see
that coming.
When Shiro bounced her shot
off of the Jibril's bullet,
she wasn't aiming for you.
Shiro:
I was aiming below.
Sora:
At Steph, who was being carried
by one of the animal girls.
That's absurd!
Sora:
NPC movement is
controlled by certain rules.
Shiro:
As a result, you can predict
where they'll be.
Sora:
And NPCs, they don't make
any sound when they walk.
And since Steph
was unconscious,
you couldn't sense
her desire to attack you.
That means you weren't
going to detect her.
Also, before the game,
I bound Steph
with the pledges to obey
any order that Shiro
had written on the ground,
but to forget that order
as soon as she read it.
"Once your love power
is restored,
wait until your energy
is just about to run out,
and then fire
straight ahead."
Shiro:
All we had to do was
calculate the NPC's movements
and then lead Izuna
to the predicted spot.
Ino:
Impossible, that's not
a matter of mere calculation.
That's like...
Sora:
Seeing the future, right?
Why, it's almost like
I read your mind, isn't it?
This whole game,
you've been tracking
our heartbeats and pointing
out our positions to Izuna.
Ino:
They knew that we were
doing this all the time
and took advantage of it!
Sora:
When it comes down to it,
there are really
only two actions
you can take in a game.
Shiro:
Advance your own strategy
or to respond to another
player's strategy.
It's a question
of who has the initiative.
Sora:
And in this case,
we held the initiative
throughout the entire game,
that's all there is to it.
You thought you were
making all the moves
when in fact we were
playing you like fools.
It wasn't precognition
on our part.
The result
was simply inevitable.
You see, the weak have
their own way of fighting.
( chuckles )
We leave it to the strong
to fight each other head‐on.
It's not our style.
All right, how about
you tell everybody
who the winner is, Gramps?
( grunting angrily )
Ino:
The winner is Elkia.
And so in accordance
with the pledges,
the Eastern Federation
turns over everything
on the continent
to the kingdom of Elkia.
( cheering )
Sora, why did you
deliberately alter your shot
and aim for my panties?
Sora:
Don't ask that!
You know the answer!
Couldn't let all these people
see my little sister naked!
Oh, yeah, well what about me?
Does my dignity mean nothing?
Now, now, don't get upset.
You won us the victory, Dolly.
You're everyone's hero now.
Oh, and good work
from you, too.
You pulled everything off
exactly according to plan.
But of course, I aim to please
you however I can, Master.
Izuna:
But now‐
but now the Eastern
Federation is‐
the Warbeasts are‐
Izuna, it's not
your fault, my dear.
Our country chose to do this.
You were simply
following my orders.
Sora:
That's not it, is it, Izuna?
You're probably a little
confused right now
because you actually enjoyed
our little game, didn't you?
No, I would never,
ever feel that way.
So many people
are going to suffer because‐
because I lost today.
But, Izuna...
you were smiling,
weren't you?
Why‐why did I have to go
and smile like that, thank you?
Because I did,
the Eastern Federation
will be taken over
and so many people will‐
and it's all my fault
for having too much fun
and not winning.
Sora:
It'll be okay.
Whether you had fun or not,
we would've won anyway.
So how does it feel to know
that there's an enemy out there
that you can't defeat
no matter how hard you try?
I'll tell you how it feels.
Both:
It's awesome.
You'll see.
Sora:
Your first loss hurt,
I get that,
but that's why it was fun.
Now that you know
how that feels,
you can be our friend.
Welcome, Izuna, you're
officially a gamer now.
Next time,
I'm not gonna lose, please.
Sora:
You seem to have the wrong idea
about this, by the way.
Nobody's gonna die,
and nobody's going to suffer.
This world really
is a game, you know.
No one here seems
to get that, but we do.
Kurami:
This is the power
of Imanity's weakness,
the wisdom to see the world
with unclouded eyes
and predict the future.
Okay, I think I can
have faith in that.
Fiel, were heading home.
We've got lots of work
ahead of us.
Sounds simply lovely.
( children laughing,
crowd cheering )
I really hate baths,
thank you.
I totally agree, but right now,
you're all mine.
How nice, you're really
into this today, Master.
As soon as I saw
Izuna's fluffy tail,
I just had to give her...
Tickles! ( laughs )
My, the two of you
are getting along
surprisingly well now,
aren't you?
The way things
were after the game,
I wouldn't have thought
you would become friends.
Sora had a talk
with Izuna afterwards
and straightened things out.
Shiro:
He told her
why nobody will suffer
even if the Eastern Federation
is absorbed into Elkia.
And why is that?!
Huh?
What lies did you tell
my sweet Izuna
to gain her trust,
you Goddamn ape?
What's wrong, pal?
You can't handle the truth?
Come again?
Forget I said anything.
Even if I told you,
there's nothing you could do.
Besides...
Guys, it's terrible!
The Eastern Federation!
The Eastern Fe‐
( screams ) Ugh!
Before the game with us
even started,
the Eastern Federation moved
all its special technology
and personnel off the continent,
that right?
You knew already?
Well, I just figured
since I'd do the same thing.
So why didn't you stop them
or at least say something?
We managed to take back
the continent,
but that's a serious blow.
Don't worry about it.
Our game with them
still hasn't finished yet.
Has it...
representative of the
Eastern Federation?
( laughs )
You look like you're having
a splendid time.
Would you mind
if I joined you for a bit?
( gasps )
Sh‐Shrine‐
the shrine priestess.
Nice to meet you.
Hope I'm not intruding.
Welcome to the land
beyond the sea,
where we read poetry
under the light of the moon.
Ino:
Are you sure you wish to
allow those hairless chimps
into our inner sanctum?
I don't see why not.
The game's over,
so what harm could it do?
Sora:
Is it okay if I take pictures?
Can I?! Huh?!
She's a dignitary
from another country.
Could you be polite
for once in your lives?
You two have really given us
an awful lot of trouble.
Hmm? ( laughs )
Well, That's Elves for ya.
They were faster
than I thought they'd be.
Ino:
The Elves?
What are you
talking about?
If we moved all the people
and goods off the continent,
you couldn't make good use
of your newfound territory.
That way, you'd eventually
challenge us again.
Sora:
And then you could
destroy us for good.
Or so that's what you thought.
Indeed.
Who could have guessed
you'd try to use a spy
to contact the Elves
and expose our game?
Then everyone
would know our secret,
and we wouldn't be able
to win any longer.
Shrine Priestess:
Luckily...
I had already
taken that into account.
To be honest, I had assumed
that you were working in league
with Elven Gard
from the very beginning.
But now this problem.
Avant Heim was not supposed
to be involved.
What?! How long have you
been planning this?
You wouldn't guess
by looking at me,
but I was an official there
on the Council of
18 Wings, that is.
I have a formidable degree
of influence in Avant Heim.
First we had Elkia,
then Elven Gard,
and now Avant Heim.
Even with our tricks exposed,
we would have still been able
to take on the puny
likes of Imanity,
but with the Elves
and the Flugel as well,
I'm afraid that's
another matter.
What a mess this is.
Here's what I'll do.
As representative
of the Eastern Federation,
I'm taking revenge
on you right now.
( screams )
Priestess, no!
Shall I say it again?
You've caused me an
awful lot of trouble.
Your death will
not be painless.
All righty then.
I accept your challenge.
Hmm? Uh...
I'm sick of coming up
with convoluted strategies.
Why don't we go ahead and
settle this with a coin toss?
( laughs )
That too dull?
Oh, no.
It's just this
kingdom's success,
it's my life's work,
and it's being destroyed
by shaved monkeys?
And to think it's all
coming down a coin toss?
It's hilarious.
( laughs )
I knew it. You're a gamer,
too, aren't you?
Okay, if I win,
Elkia gets all the Eastern
Federation's territory,
including the islands
outlying the continent.
And if I win the toss,
the Warbeasts get the right
to self rule and a guarantee
of resources from the mainland.
For all your talk of revenge,
you're more concerned about
preserving your people's safety.
Well, you see,
once the Elves invade,
it's over for us anyway.
This is the least I can do
given the situation.
Promise me even if
I lose this game,
Izuna and Ino
and all of my people
will be under
your protection.
Oh, Priestess.
Of course.
You're not so bad.
Yes, yes, can we begin?
Sora:
All right, let's have
the most hard‐core coin toss
ever recorded in history.
I'll let you pick.
Which one do you want,
heads or tails?
I'll just go
with whatever you don't.
Are you sure?
Yes, Ma'am.
Ready?
Both:
Achente!
( roars )
Blood Destruction!
Now I can free myself
from all physical boundaries
and begin to grasp
all the subtle nuances
in the environment.
At the rate the coin
is currently falling,
I predict that it will hit
the ground after 142 flips,
bounce four times,
spin 5.2 seconds,
and land on tails.
Hmm.
I don't detect
any magic in the vicinity.
Did they underestimate
my kinetic vision?
No, I seriously doubt that.
Although...
I pick tails.
Ino:
You gotta be shitting me.
Shiro:
A draw.
What, for real?
Oh, boy! Isn't that
something else?
Sure didn't see that
coming, eh? What a pickle.
Do we both win
or do we both lose?
Sora:
Hmm, which could it be?
Sora, you're not
fooling anybody, dummy.
Of course.
This was your goal
from the start.
You know, if we both win,
then that could mean
both of our demands
are fulfilled.
If so, you'd end up
under Elkia's control,
but your rights
are assured
and you keep the
ability to self rule.
Then we could both share
the continent's resources.
Shiro:
The Eastern Federation
becomes the Elkia Federation.
Well then, do we both win
or do we both lose?
Which one?
Don't listen to him!
He wants to take
the Eastern Federation
and destroy the Warbeasts!
Ino, you've got
it all wrong, thanks.
I beg your pardon, Sir, but what
could possibly possess me
to bring harm to my newfound
animal‐girl paradise?!
It's filled to the brim
with adorable little kitty
and puppy and fox girls
like Izuna!
Why the hell would I ever want
to destroy a treasure like that?
Dude, rein it in.
Shrine Priestess:
Honestly...
to think that we've been playing
into your hands this whole time.
However, even if our nations
do unite, thanks to you,
the Elves now know
all our secrets.
Elven Gard will declare
war on us eventually.
You're right,
and when they do,
how about we make them regret
they made that decision?
You honestly think
you can do that?
Hell, yeah, I can.
The thing about that spy?
She actually had her memories
altered by the pledges
before she reported
to the Elven Gard,
so she gave them the wrong
information about your game.
So then the reason
you fought Kurami
for the right to alter
her memories, that was...
Shiro:
It was for this very day.
Now when Elven Gard attacks us,
we're sure to win against them.
Then we get to claim
the Elves' nation, too.
You're telling me you thought
this through that far?
Checkmate doesn't mean you've
simply cornered the enemy king.
It's a declaration
that the enemy king is yours.
That's why I said it
the first time I met you.
Check and mate. Get it?
( gasps )
Okay, so which will it be?
Do we both win,
or do we both lose?
It's all up to you.
Are you really
gonna make me say it?
Okay, fine.
Have it your way.
We both win.
Okay, good deal.
Sora and Shiro:
The Elkia Federation is born.
Shrine Priestess:
So what you plan to do now?
Please don't tell me
you're thinking
about starting
another Great War.
If I wanted that,
I would've taken
your race piece.
But those must never be taken,
so we won't.
That's right.
Our goal has never changed.
It's simple and straightforward.
Both:
We must defeat Tet.
And that's it.
Defeat Tet? How?
But he's God.
That's not possible.
Oh, yeah, why not?
Yeah, why not?
( laughs )
Shrine Priestess:
Oh, you're going
to try to beat a God?
My, you do come up
with the strangest ideas.
You actually think
you can do it?
Shiro:
Don't know.
Sora:
We don't have any clues
about the specifics,
but we have some hints.
Like here, why are the race
pieces shaped the way they are?
Shiro:
And then...
Sora:
Why are there precisely
16 races of Exceed
in this world,
not more or less?
Shiro:
And finally...
Sora:
What are those things
I see on the horizon?
So you think that gathering
all the pieces
is what gives you the right
to challenge God?
But wait, doesn't that mean
you need to take
each of our race pieces
to play the game?
Sora:
I doubt it.
'Cause you see, that would go
against the pledges.
Why do you
think that?
Simple‐ why put in a rule that
doesn't have to be followed?
Shiro:
Maybe you forgot.
Steph:
Forgot what?
Sora:
Pledge number ten of course,
perhaps the most important one.
Let's all have fun
and play together!
Sora:
In other words,
if we're not all together
having fun,
we can't beat the game.
You see, we don't need
to steal each other's pieces.
Like the legend says,
each of the races,
the 16 races
who call themselves wise,
must use their
ingenuity and wit,
their great fortunes and power,
to build a tower
of knowledge on Disboard.
Prove to me
your strength of mind.
I'm not asking for
that much from you, right?
( laughs )
That's great!
Wonderful!
This really is getting fun.
I was so right
to bring those two here.
I'm waiting for you!
We'll have the best game ever!
Bring all your
friends along, too!
Until then...
Kurami:
Elven Gard, the largest
country in the world,
and we're supposed
to tear it apart from within.
He makes it sound
like that's easy.
Oh, I'm sure he
has a plan.
Well, if he does, I'd like
to know what it is.
I guess we'll come up
with something.
Otherwise, Imanity doesn't
really stand a chance.
It'll work out.
A way for the weak
to defeat a strong
while remaining weak,
a way to stay who you are
but at the same time
surpass your limits,
to soar through the sky even
though you don't have wings.
Despite all the despair,
suffering, and darkness,
he's always managed
to find a path of the light.
I knew I wasn't just
imagining things.
Something about you
has changed, Kurami.
Yeah?
I guess Sora's confidence
is wearing off on me.
And if I have you,
then I can do anything.
( laughs )
And I'll be happy
to help out.
I would take on
the entire world for you,
which might actually
be the case.
Kurami:
( laughs )
You may be right.
Well, let's see
what we can do.
Well, we'd better
get going.
Steph:
Oh, thank goodness.
What about
the other thingy?
Don't worry,
I hadn't forgotten.
Huh? Um, forgotten
about what?
Thought of something else
to try and take away
from our Priestess?!
Think again, Primate!
It's not really
something we want, per se.
If you're a shrine priestess,
you must have one, right?
Shiro:
We've been wondering
if you could call it.
Oh.
What did she just do?!
What's going on?!
What an amazing level
of power.
( echoing )
Divine core manifestation,
mind meld established.
Power setting minimal.
Why have you summoned me,
you creatures
of the finite lifespans?
Exceed rank number one...
the Old Deus.
Exceed rank... one?
Old...
Old Deus!
Okay.
Sora and Shiro:
Let the games begin.