Shiro:
Once upon a time,
a little girl was sent
to an institution
before she was one year old
because of her
super intelligence.
She would learn
many new things there
like how to walk
and how to speak.
It was then that she was
introduced to games as well.
She was made to play many games
they called intelligence tests,
but they were so boring
that she didn't enjoy them
no matter
who she played with.
And then after two years
had passed,
she was reunited
with a woman
whom she was told
was her mother...
as well is a boy who was
seven years older than her.
The boy told The adults
whatever they wanted to hear
and grinned at everyone
with a fake, empty smile.
The girl said to him,
the first words she had spoken
in a long, long time...
You seem so empty.
Sora:
( chuckles )
So, you want to play a game?
Who's Sora?
Blank...
Blank does not..
Blank does not...
( whimpering )
( screams )
Oh, dear, you must've
had a really bad dream.
I'll bring you a glass
of warm milk.
Does that sound okay?
No, no!
He was with me!
He's always been with me!
That's why‐
Shiro.
Shiro!
It's cold.
Master? That's
where you were.
Dolly was panicking and said
that you ran off somewhere,
so I was wondering
what could have happened.
Jibril.
Yes, can I help you
with something?
Tell me the names
of your masters.
Huh? Is this some
sort of game?
I don't know
why you would‐
Answer me!
You are my
only master.
Then who was it
that made me your master?
Jibril:
Well, it was you,
of course.
Shiro:
But... Then who told Stephanie
to fall in love with them?
Jibril:
It was you, Mistress Shiro.
Shiro:
Who found out about the
Eastern Federation's games?
Jibril:
You, Mistress Shiro,
with the help
of what Dolly's grandfather
left behind.
It was all you.
I was charmed by your
unparalleled brilliance
right from the beginning.
That's why I decided
to obey you, Master.
Obey me?
Yes.
Jibril:
Only you, Mistress Shiro,
Queen of Elkia,
and representative of Imanity.
Steph:
So she's saying that there
was somebody else besides her?
Jibril:
But there's no sign
of this somebody.
I expanded my range of inquiry
to the entire city
in addition to the castle
to no avail.
Yeah, no one in the
protest demonstration
seems to know anything
about him either.
Yes, I was afraid of that.
It seems as though master
must have played a game
with someone
unbeknownst to us.
She then lost and had
her memories altered.
Steph:
That's impossible,
there's no one who could‐
( gasps )
The Eastern Federation.
Jibril:
Yes, they are
capable of that.
Master?
Let's play a game.
Uh...
( door opens )
A game?
Yes, we can just bet
the false memories
that have been implanted
inside you, okay, Miss?
False memories?
And I know it's very rude
to ask of you,
but would you please lose?
All right then,
that's a check.
Shiro:
False memories.
But they...
seem so real.
Are they true or not?
Is that why
they're disappearing?
( crying )
Shiro...
They say anyone
can change their fate.
Wonder if that's true.
Shiro:
They're all...
all disappearing.
Sora:
If someone decides
they want to fly,
will they suddenly
sprout wings?
I don't think so.
You can't change what you are.
You can just change
how you do things.
Sora?
You have to make
your own way.
You have to create a way to fly
even while you stay the same.
That's how you survive.
Let's think of
something together, okay,
a way to give you wings.
No need to hurry.
Shiro:
They're all...
fake memories...
all of them, lies.
If they disappear,
I'll feel...
( mouthing words )
"You're... Blank"?
Master?
Shiro:
Blank does not‐
Blank doesn't‐
Blank does not lose!
Jibril:
Why... did you win,
Mistress Shiro?
He's real!
Sora is real!
I know!
I know he's real!
Shiro...
Master, please
calm down.
He's real!
He is real!
Jibril:
Just slow down, Master.
Try to think through
this logically.
Steph:
You're right.
I mean, it absolutely
does make more sense
to think he doesn't exist,
but somehow I feel in my heart
that he really does.
But Dolly, he doesn't.
Besides, I couldn't
imagine you losing.
So it must be
something else.
Oh, Steph.
Then where
is he?
Yeah, he's gotta
be here somewhere!
There must be some reason
why this happened,
some reason
why we can't remember.
Jibril:
Come now, you're
being ridiculous,
This doesn't
make sense.
Shiro:
Hey, guys?
What did we do yesterday?
Uh... yesterday?
I was busy dealing
with the demonstrations.
After that, you played a game
in the throne room.
That was the day
before yesterday, the 19th.
Let me rephrase my question.
Do you remember
where you were two nights ago?
Okay, let's see,
now think,
what was I doing
the night before last?
Well, um, I‐ huh?
I can't remember.
Right, none of us can.
Huh...?
Now let me see.
Mmm!
Well, this is... different.
Well, Steph,
do you like this or not?
Excuse me, how am I supposed
to respond to that, exactly?
You don't like it?
Even though I made you
fall in love with me?
Not really.
So you're saying that
someone other than you
must have told you to fall
in love with them, right?
Yes, it was my brother Sora
who told her that.
Okay, but didn't
you already decide
that he existed
without this test?
Yeah, that's right,
so why did you
just totally grope me
if you already knew that?
I, uh... wanted to be sure.
Thanks a lot, Steph.
You were a big help.
Oh, sure.
Then let's think hard
about this.
If Sora actually exists
somewhere,
then how could he
have disappeared?
He wasn't just taken away.
Our memories of both him
and the last day and a half
have all vanished, too.
A large‐scale magic spell
could conceivably do
something like that,
but it would've left
some traces of being cast.
What if it was a game?
A game?
What if the rules are altering
our perception of reality?
It's possible
because of the pledges.
Hmm, if the game involved
Imanity's representative,
then I suppose it's possible
that the rules
would be able to affect
the entire race,
but it shouldn't work on Jibril,
should it?
No, because Sora's
my master now,
he should be
my representative, too.
We can assume I'm under
the same effects as well.
Okay, I guess that makes sense,
but if that's the case,
then what kind of game
are we talking about?
I don't know.
But I know what...
Sora said to me.
You know
that I believe in you.
Shiro, never forget
the two of us are always one.
Sora would never leave me
all by myself.
So...
Sora: ( weakly )
Shiro, where are you?
You're still there,
right, Shiro?
Sora?
Steph and Jibril:
Huh?
Sora:
Would you just hold
on to me somewhere,
anywhere that I can still feel?
I'm losing my mind in here.
Sora!
Shiro?
Shiro:
It's time to use every last
brain cell I've got.
What's really going on here?
Come on,
Sora trusted me with this.
I've got to try and use
all the memories I still have.
Sora said that we're
always together,
so he must be here somewhere.
And he said that the game
is always won
before it even begins.
He was trying
to prepare me for this.
( gasps )
He told me the two of us
are not like comic book heroes.
No, I've got to
think harder! Harder!
He said he was going to get
the last piece we needed.
Get the piece we needed?
Then this game is to get us
something we need
before we can face
the Eastern Federation.
A tool? A strategy?
An observer. An Elf?
He's going to get an Elf,
but how?
Challenge Elven Gard?
Kurami?
No, Kurami
doesn't believe in Sora.
She'd never agree to help us.
( gasps )
What if the game...
was to steal each other's being?
Shiro! Shiro!
A game to steal
each other's existence?
That's right.
These 32 stones collectively
make up your existence.
They're individually numbered
and ranked
in order of importance.
Their priority is assigned
to them by your subconscious.
So in other words neither of us
can consciously know
which of these stones
constitutes which part
of ourselves until our opponent
has taken it away.
What importance
does your subconscious place
on that elf next to you?
Or your arms, legs, nerves,
or memories, for that matter?
In the end, your very
existence is taken
and no one will even realize
that you're there.
In other words,
you'll disappear.
Kurami:
Are you serious?
Uh‐huh.
Pledge number five,
the challenged party
has the right to decide
the rules of the game.
If you don't like it,
the game is off.
What do you say?
Kurami‐
Fiel, you realize
this man is saying
that he's willing to bet
Imanity's race piece?
Kurami:
We can't simply
ignore that.
( chuckles )
Look, honestly, I was sort
of hoping that we'd be able
to possibly reconcile
after what happened.
Sora:
Oh, we can reconcile
but to do that,
first you gotta trust me
and give me that elf.
You know that's not
gonna happen.
I guess you're right.
What exactly
are you betting?
Let's say the winner
gets the right to make
two demands of the loser.
One could, for example,
make the results
of the game eternal,
erasing the other's
existence permanently.
Then they could
alter the memories
of the loser's partner to make
them their ally instead.
So then what you want to do here
is bet not only our partners
but our existence as well?
Sora:
That's right.
You are just insane.
( laughs )
Well, then, since I'm apparently
out of my mind already,
I'll go ahead and impose
one more important rule.
Sora?
Master?
Shiro, are you
feeling okay?!
Sora!
Jibril?
How can I
help you, Master?
In a game, could you steal
someone else's existence?
No, I don't
think you could.
It's only possible in a
fake world like the one
we used to play
word chain.
Shiro:
What if an Elf helped you?
An Elf?
Those disgusting
little forest creatures?
Why, during the great war,
I easily destroyed
one of their capital cities‐
Shiro:
But could you?
I suppose
it is possible.
Gross and weak as they are,
those animals do have
some small measure
of skill when it comes
to constructing complicated
spells at least.
Then what you're saying
is that this Sora guy
managed to erase his own
existence by playing this game?
Yes.
But if he's been erased,
then wouldn't it mean the game's
over and he's already lost?
What else could it
mean otherwise?
Yeah, that's true,
if he won, he would exist,
and we wouldn't be worrying
about this in the first place.
Shiro:
What if it was
neither of those?
You think the game's
still being played now?
Mm‐hmm.
That can't be.
Jibril, see if you can detect
any magic in this room.
I understand, Master.
Shiro:
I woke up here
in this room.
Even though my brother
and I sleep somewhere else,
this is where I woke up.
Sora always said
he would never leave me alone.
You're right,
magic is being used here.
But I can't tell
from what exactly.
Okay, we just have
to search everywhere
until we can find
something! ( screams )
Jibril:
Oh, dear, you just tripped
over literally nothing, Dolly.
You aren't obligated
to embarrass yourself.
How'd that happen?
Something was there.
An Othello disc? Hmm.
That says "three"
in the Elf language.
Jibril:
Why are there discs
but no board?
Shiro:
Because they haven't
been played yet.
If they're still here,
then I can play.
Yeah, but even
if that's the case,
all we have here are
two sets of three discs.
There isn't any way
for us to know if we're
playing black or white.
It's simple.
Sora said that we're one.
The two of us are one player,
and I'm still participating
in this game.
Sora:
This rule is very important.
Each of our partners
will play in the game as well.
If one of us can't
continue to play,
our partner
can play for us.
That's why I still
kept some memories.
Then can you see it,
the playing board?
I can't.
But I... know what
Sora would do next...
What is this?
You're deliberately trying
to lose, aren't you?
No, I've set it up so I can
still win like this.
Shiro:
How he would lead
his opponent on.
Hmm? What happened?
Are these were memories?
Does that mean you're making me
steal your memories
to prove that you're not using
the magic abilities
of another race to win games?
That's not such
a bad answer.
Shiro:
How he would tell me
what he wants...
Kurami:
Now he can't
continue the game.
I won then, I guess.
Then why is the
game still here?
Huh? What is going on?
Shouldn't the match have ended?
Kurami:
There's three left.
What parts of Sora
do they represent?
Shiro:
How he would deceive
his opponent, and then...
how he'd be able to win.
Sora, you're amazing.
Nobody would be able
to figure this out.
Nobody but us.
Now I understand.
I know what parts of you
are contained in these discs.
Three,
the way to win this game.
Two, the absolute faith
you have in your little sister.
And the last one...
everything I am to you.
Now please...
come back to me!
SORA!
Oh...
( gasps and coughs )
We did it.
Shiro...
Okay! You can punch me
if you want!
Give me your best shot!
Let me have it!
( Shiro whimpers )
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Sora! I should
have come sooner!
( crying )
I can't believe I actually
forgot my master.
I'm still so confused.
Fiel:
Kurami!
Please wake up! Kurami!
Can you hear me?
Oh, say something.
Now then,
since I'm the victor,
it is time for me
to make my demands.
Please, please
I beg you, you can do
whatever you want with me,
just don't hurt Kurami.
Yeah, whatever.
Demand number one.
Please, no!
We keep a copy
of the memories we stole
from each other
and return the originals.
Huh?
( gasps )
Kurami.
Steph:
Wait, what's going on?
They each get to keep
the memories
they took from one another,
but they all get their own
memories back as well.
Jibril:
Now Kurami Sora know
everything about each other
so there's no need
for distrust.
In other words,
they can work together without
having to wonder about what
the other's motivations are.
This is the last piece
that he had been looking for.
Demand number two,
I want you, Elf.
Fiel, I'm gonna
reserve the right
to alter your memories
as I please.
Wha‐
Don't worry.
It's fine, Fiel. He only
wants one thing from us.
Kurami:
If I'm not mistaken,
you need us to spy for you.
Yeah, you got it.
Sounds like we're both on
the same wavelength already.
But spies? What does
he want us to spy on?
Mmm, oh, I'll
tell you later.
Kurami:
After seeing
what was in your head,
I changed my mind
about you.
You can count on me.
( laughs )
Shiro:
You're amazing, Sora.
Hmm? Aren't I!
Tell me how proud you are
of your big brother.
Come on,
don't be shy now.
Mm‐hmm.
So proud of you.
You're my hero.
( laughs ) Oh, shucks,
when you put it like that,
it really
makes me blush!
Oh!
Master?
Shiro... are you
ready to do this?
Yeah.
I'll be standing by.
Any time is okay.
Fiel...
Kurami...
( all inhale deeply )
Oh, my God, I was so scared!
I'm never doing that again!
( all sobbing )
What's wrong with them?
Are they okay?
They like to put on
such a tough show all the time.
Jibril:
But they have
a sensitive side, too.
Steph:
( mechanically )
All your base are belong to us.
Sora:
Shut up!
Steph:
I know all the memes, yay!