What the heck
is going on here?
Huh, what? this?
Well, in case
you didn't catch on,
we're siblings,
so don't get the wrong idea.
Oh, rejected
by my own brother.
I don't care about
your stupid relationship!
I'm asking you why
you didn't call that girl out
if you knew she was totally
trying to cheat me back there!
Now I've blown my chance
at ruling the kingdom!
Pledge eight states‐
"Being caught cheating
during a game
is grounds for
an instant loss," right?
Yeah, duh!
And now thanks to you,
some nobody is gonna
take over my kingdom.
My life is over!
So, basically‐
Shiro:
She lost her match
to the cheater,
and she's a sore loser.
Sora:
She fell for it.
Let me get this straight.
You got totally hustled,
lost all your worldly
possessions,
and somehow that's supposed
to be our fault?
What was that?!
Ha, whatever, toots.
Not only that,
when you get called out on it,
you completely flip out
and start yapping
like a little dog.
Pull it together.
You're an emotional time bomb,
too unstable
to think logically
and too scared
to take any risks.
Let me ask you,
does crazy run in your family?
Or are you just
a natural loser?
( sobs )
Hmm...
You take that back,
right... now.
Huh?
Say what you want about me,
but I will not tolerate such
insults against my grandfather!
You take that back
this instant!
Well, I'm right about
that explosive temper,
a foolish king
and a foolish granddaughter.
Stephanie:
I said that's enough!
( claps )
Then how about a game?
( theme song plays )
A game?
Yeah,
aren't all conflicts
supposed to be resolved
through games?
That's like this world's
second rule, right?
So how's a game
of rock‐paper‐scissors sound?
You want to play that?
Yeah, but one thing.
It's simple.
I'll only play paper.
(gasps)
So I can only win this game
if I play paper.
( trumpet fanfare )
But say I beat you
at rock or scissors,
you'll lose, too,
so it ends up being a tie.
Stephanie:
Then what happens if we both
play the same thing?
Sora:
In that case,
it still ends up being a tie,
but if you can play
anything besides paper,
you can actually win.
Easy enough for you?
Stephanie:
Oh, I get it.
So that's the trick.
I'm in.
So what are we betting?
How about if you win,
whatever you wish
will be my command.
I'll tell you how
you were cheated,
and if you're still mad
about me dissing your
stupid old grandfather so much
you can have us put to death.
Do what?!
But if I win the game,
you'll be on my leash,
of course.
It's a high stakes game
or rock‐paper‐scissors
with my life on the line.
Fair enough for you?
And if we tie?
Then I'll just give you a hint
about our cheating methods.
in exchange,
you can do me a tiny favor.
I'm getting worried
'cause when this gold runs out,
we're more or less gonna
be hobos on this planet.
So you're saying you want me
to give you a place to stay.
Mmm...
Fine.
Then challenge excepted.
I swear by the pledges.
Aschente!
Aschente it is!
Stephanie:
Ha! I'm not gonna fall
for his trap that easily.
He might be trying
to convince me
that his rules give me
the advantage,
but there's still
a one‐in‐three chance
that the game
ends in a draw.
Basically,
he's shooting for a tie,
so he wins
a place to stay.
Sorry to disappoint you,
smarty pants,
but victory won't come
that easy.
Even with these rules
if I just play rock
I have a two‐in‐three chance
of winning.
Same as scissors,
also a two‐in‐three chance.
But with paper, I only have
a one‐in‐three chance to win,
So my best chance is throwing
scissors or rock.
But since he said
he'd only play paper,
that makes it more risky
on my end to play rock,
which is the only way
he can win.
In other words,
he's trying to force me
to play scissors.
Ha! So much
for your genius ploy.
Did you really think I was
stupid enough to fall for that?
I'll crush your plans
and play rock!
No, wait a minute!
Let's think about this,
Stephanie Dola.
There's a two‐in‐three chance
I'll win if I play rock,
but there's also a one‐in‐three
chance I'll lose.
So, wait a minute.
Unless he's totally lying,
he said he'd only play paper.
So if he does,
then he'll risk a one‐in‐three
chance of losing
as well as a one‐in‐three
chance of winning.
But if he doesn't,
he'll have a two‐in‐three
chance of losing
and absolutely no chance
of winning.
Since that's the case,
there shouldn't be any reason
for him to play anything else.
It's obvious.
He's got to pick... paper.
Ready? Here we go.
Yeah, I'm ready.
Sora:
One, two...
Stephanie:
But I hope
Sora:
Shoot!
( whimpers )
I'll admit, good try.
But not good enough.
You probably thought
I was gonna try to goad you
into playing rock,
but once you saw my expression
you realized I couldn't win
unless I played
anything but paper.
I'll give you that much.
You did actually end up
blocking me from winning.
But still, your best bet
would have been paper.
Yeah, but with scissors,
I could double my chances
to win compared to paper.
Of course, that's how I knew
you'd end up picking scissors.
You were so busy trying
to get inside my head,
you didn't think that
I was in yours.
Otherwise, you would
have wised up
and played paper
for the win.
See, I told you‐
you're just not good enough.
Oh, don't be so hard
on yourself,
the results were pretty
much a given.
Sorry,
but you had no chance.
Fine, I get it.
You were trying to
corner me into a tie.
I'll find you housing.
No, that's all right.
Hey, Sis, what did I say
my prize would be?
Shiro:
If you won,
she'd owe you a tiny favor.
And I said that favor was?
Didn't say.
Oh, w‐wait a minute!
That's not true!
I know I asked if
you wanted a place to stay
before we started
Yep, but do you remember
my response?
Uh...
( gasps )
No...
That's right.
Those were my words, not his.
He just complained
about money.
I guess you didn't notice,
but this game's big catch
was that whether
you lost or tied,
the risk was gonna
be the same.
No fair!
That's cheating!
Hey, I stuck to the rules
of the pledges
when I laid the game
out for you.
Sora:
Why should I take blame
if you didn't get it?
So since I'm sure
you're wondering...
(menacing)
why don't I
tell you the favor?
I want you...
...to love me!
Huh?
( echoes )
To love me!
( laughs )
( cackles )
What do you think, Sis?
Your brother came up
with the perfect plan!
Pledge number six‐
any bets made in accordance
with the pledges
must be upheld.
All I have to do is make
her fall in love with me
and we'd be in her palace
and rolling in riches.
Uh, you could
have had all of that
if you'd just said,
"give me all of your stuff."
Say what?
Shiro:
Sora...
you succumbed
to your desires.
( stammers )
I did what?
( shouts )
You mean after all the genius
work I've put into my plan,
I was thwarted by
my not‐so‐subconscious fear
of being a virgin
the rest of my life?!
Even when faced against
my mighty brain,
you're telling me,
Little Sora, down in my pants...
But you said you never
wanted a girlfriend.
Remember, you said
all you needed was me.
Shiro...
( groans )
Sora:
I was just trying to look cool
when I said that.
It was a lie!
It's not like
I can date my sister.
You're only 11, anyway.
I'm a healthy
and virile young man
and a man's got sexual needs
and sexual needs
AND sexual needs.
Did I mention sexual needs?
Shiro:
Yeah, you said it four times
already.
Steph:
I know the ten pledges are set
in stone,
but... am I really jealous
that he's gushing
over his sister
and ignoring me?
I mean, we just met.
No! It's nonsense.
( shouts )
I'll never love you!
( growls )
Sora:
( chuckles ) Baby.
( screams )
No way! There's no way
I'm feeling this.
Falling in love is just
some chemical imbalance, right?
It's just an illusion.
( screams and sobs )
Come on, stay strong.
(gravelly) Fight it!
Fight the urges!
Sora:
Hey, mind if I call you
Steph, from now on?
That would be wonderful!
No, no, no, no, no,
this isn't right!
What the hell
is wrong with me?!
(screams)
Uh, hey, Steph?
Uh‐huh?
Are you good with us
staying in the palace?
But, of course!
( sobs )
Wow, those pledges
really have a hold
on these people,
don't they?
Sora?
Yo!
You're losing your virginity.
Congrats.
Uh...
( gasps )
My cute body isn't ready
for defiling.
...is happening
in front of you!
( gasps )
Shiro:
Why? I'm cool with it.
Well, as your brother,
I'm not!
One's, youth should be
wholesome and healthy.
Shiro:
Why don't you see
how healthy she is?
( groans )
(thud)
Accidental boob grab.
Nice move.
It was an accident!
(surprised moan)
So soft, voluptuous.
Steph:
(irritated)
He's touching me!
Shiro:
And now the moment we've all
been waiting for...
Sora:
(deep tone)
The pantaloons.
( whimpers )
Please, you have to...
(screaming)
get off me!
( panting )
Stephanie:
Oh, Sora! I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Sora:
I swear, I'm really sorry.
I'll never touch boobs again.
I promise I'll never touch any
girl again. Please forgive me,
I just thought this might be
the only chance in my life
to ever lay hands
on any boobies anywhere.
I mean, hentai games
and oppai mousepads...
Did he get brain damaged
or wh‐ ( screams )
Sora, where are you?
Please don't leave me here.
I don't want to be alone.
I'm scared.
Where did you go? You can't
abandon me in this scary place.
Please, Sora,
where are you?
You've got to be kidding me.
This is what happens
when you two
are apart from each other?
A couple of weirdos.
Sora!
Shiro!
Both:
Hug!
Okay, I'm done.
You two are freaks.
Steph:
So you're like
aliens or something?
Sora:
Yep.
(Stephanie)
Then that's why you're trying
Shiro:
You don't think
it's weird that we came
from another planet?
Stephanie:
I know there's magic
and sorcery
and other stuff like that,
so anything's possible, really.
Sora: This really
is a fantasy world.
But I guess
my real question is,
is this how your people
normally take baths?
Sora:
Well, Shiro's not
a huge fan of baths.
She hates taking them
'cause she says
the Pedo Police will take me
away for watching her.
Sora:
That's why we invited
our good old friend
Mr. Steam to help out.
No pervs allowed,
Sora.
Stephanie:
If you know
it makes her uncomfortable,
then why don't you just
wait outside?
Obviously, we can't be
too far apart from each other.
So Mr. Steam comes
in very handy.
Sora:
But don't despair, Steph,
I'll be sure to check out
your boobage.
Sora:
Oopsie!
Heya, Steph,
my hand's all slippery!
Mind picking that up for me?
Stephanie:
Uh... what is it?
Oh, it's just a secret tool
from another world.
A secret tool?
Shiro:
Oh!
Sora:
( chuckles )
As long as Steph grabs
the phone first,
I can check out her naughty
nudey nakedness
without Shiro getting
in the shot!
What's going on?
Did you grab it?
(screams)
Stephanie:
Yeah...
Shiro:
Perfect view, too. Pew pew.
It's hard to move in,
and it's so frilly.
I used to wear that
all the time
back when I was
a little kid.
Perfect fit, huh?
( gasps )
Sora:
It's a bit formal
for my taste,
but it's kind of like cosplay,
so I guess that's cool, right?
( chuckles )
My butler fantasy!
You look exquisite,
Steph, ravishing.
Oh, you.
(pop)
Huh?!
Don't be such an idiot!
Sora:
What the heck is
her problem, anyway?
Shiro:
Maybe herself?
( screams )
I'll be right back.
Better go make some tea!
(giggle)
( door slams )
That was really weird.
Sora, you really don't
get girls, do you?
Um, Miss, wait.
Hold on, Miss.
Perhaps, you should
let us make the tea?
Don't worry about me!
Um, Ma'am, why are
you dressed like a hobo?
Maybe she's sick.
Call a doctor!
Simply delicious.
You're quite the cook,
aren't you, sweet cheeks?
Sora, you should
totally marry her.
( snickers )
Stephanie:
Huh, your wife?!
Oh, my, I'm embarrassed!
Miss Dola no!
Please stop!
( screams )
Okay, keep your wits
about you, Stephanie Dola.
You can't let him undo
you with his unworldly wiles.
I'm sorry
if I kept you waiting.
What the?
Sora?
Uh...
Sora:
You'd never guess
there's a tournament
to find the next king
by the looks of this place.
It's like a ghost town.
Hm?
So what the hell
language is that?
Shiro:
Not sure.
Stephanie:
There used to be a time
when Elkia was the largest
of all the Imanity nations.
And what's Imanity?
That's the human race.
Oh, so, us?
Imanity once had many nations,
and they were spread
all throughout the world,
Stephanie:
But many of them
are already dying out
by the time my
grandfather took power.
Now there is only Elkia.
It's gotten to the point
where we have to gamble
our territories
in hopes of gaining
even just a little ground.
Then who else
is there to play against,
something other than humans
or Imanity or whatever?
Stephanie:
Yes, exactly.
So other aliens
like us, or what?
Well, let's see.
There are a total
of 16 sentient races
that must abide by God's
ten sacred pledges.
Collectively,
we just refer to all the races
as The Exceed
to keep it simple.
The first order
is the Old Deus
who were defeated
by the One God.
The Phantasma
are the second order
and The Elementals
are the third.
Skipping to the seventh order,
we have the Elves,
who are great at magic
and comprise the world's
largest nation.
On the lower end,
we have the Warbeasts
at number 14,
and The Sirens at the 15th‐
Sora:
Hold on a second.
What's up with the all
this order business?
It's like a ranking system.
From what I've been told,
it's determined by
a race's affinity for magic.
And what about Imanity?
Well, we're at 16.
Sora:
Dead last, huh?
Stephanie:
That's just the way
it is.
We have zero magical abilities.
Zero? So Imanity
can't use magic?
Right, unlike
the other races,
Imanity lacks
the Spirit Circuits
that would allow us to connect
to the source of all magic.
And what's worse than that,
we can't even tell
if someone else
is using magic or not.
Sora:
So you think
you can't win.
Well, you know what
they call that, don't you?
A self‐fulfilling prophecy.
Huh?
Hey, Steph,
any libraries around here?
Steph:
Uh, well, there's a bunch
of books in the study.
However...
They're all in Imanity.
We'll just have
to learn it then, won't we?
Stephanie:
Yeah, I guess so.
Shiro:
Sora?
Huh?
(book slams shut)
I learned it.
Stephanie:
Huh?
Sora:
That was fast.
Praise me more.
Yeah, way to go,
Little Sis.
She learned it?
You make me so proud of you,
you tiny little genius.
She's gotta be joking, right?
She really learned
the entire language that fast?
Yeah, so what?
But that's impossible.
It's only been like
five minutes.
Since your spoken language
is the same as ours, it's easy.
Catch up, Sora.
Sora:
Huh, a man should
take his time,
This... is totally insane.
instead of
finishing quickly.
This... is totally insane.
My, how very small of you,
Brother.
No weiner jokes!
Steph:
Wait, his
rock‐paper‐scissors scheming,
Steph:
Wait, his
rock‐paper‐scissors scheming,
her genius level intelligence,
solid teamwork,
complete trust
and confidence...
You think
you're so special...
Stephanie:
then it's possible
that these two...
...that these two could
be the ones to save Elkia!
( cheers and applause )
Man:
And the victor of this match
is Kurami Zell!
( cries )
Sora:
Steph, what made you
want to rule Elkia?
Huh?
Sora:
I stayed up all night
reading all these books.
I've learned a lot
about this kingdom
and your grandfather
and his whole story.
Oh.
Sora:
Were you scared of losing
your status in the royal family?
Steph:
No, not really.
Then it was Elkia
you wanted to save.
That's pretty much it.
Of course I have
other reasons.
In any case,
my grandfather was forced
to gamble our
country's territory,
but he kept losing.
Hence his title,
"The Foolish King."
But despite people
resenting him,
my grandfather believed
in the potential of Imanity.
He didn't care
we were the lowest ranked
or that we can't use magic,
He believed that
if we tried hard enough,
we could win somehow.
I want to show the world
that my grandfather
wasn't just some old fool.
If I can become king,
then I can take
our territory back.
Then I can prove to everyone
that my grandfather was right,
that we can win.
Tell me, Steph,
do you love this country,
this world?
Yeah...
with all of my heart.
Wow, nice.
I'm kind of jealous
you can say that
with such conviction,
but... there's no way
that wish is coming true.
Sora:
In fact, as it stands,
this country
is already doomed.
Once the next king
takes the throne,
it's all over.
Uh, Kurami?
Stephanie:
So it's time for
the coronation already, huh?
Kurami:
Well, well, Princess,
don't tell me you've been
dressing in bed sheets
ever since I beat you.
I believe I heard you say
this was the dress
that your beloved grandfather
gave you before he died.
Here, I don't need it.
Oops.
Just face it,
you lost, so move on.
It would be wise if you didn't
make the same mistakes
as the fool
who gave you that dress.
( sobs )
Sora:
You know,
if you keep acting like that
you're only gonna prove
her right.
In case you hadn't noticed,
the game's already started.
Sora?
I'm sure you know
pledge six‐
all bets made in accordance
with the pledges must be upheld.
So this dress is yours.
But just for a while, okay?
Looks like the granddaughter
of The Foolish King
has inherited some
fools for servants, too.
Hey, Shiro?
Mm?
You're gonna stick by your bro
no matter what happens?
Mm.
Shiro:
Just like I promised,
I'll follow you anywhere.
That's a good answer!
This is a pretty
miserable situation, so‐
Liar, you know
you're loving this.
Well, it sure beats
sitting at home
and now you can't say I don't
take you anywhere fun, right?
Hey, Steph, you just
gonna sit there forever?
Come on, you want
to win that dress
back from her, don't you?
Let's get going.
Hurry.
Uh...
Sora:
You ready?
But where?
We're going to prove
that your grandfather wasn't
the fool people thought.
Huh? Sora!
What's going on?
I'm not just having
another fantasy, am I?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Thanks, Steph.
Those cookies were great,
nice work.
Yum!
( gasps )
I'm so glad
you liked them!
( laughs )
Sora:
What's next?
I don't know.
Being king might be fun.
( theme song plays )
Sora:
You still like your sheet
dress, Steph?
Steph:
I never liked it!