Welcome, I'm the one
they call Jibril.
You are King Sora
and Queen Shiro?
What business
do the new rulers
of Imanity have with me?
Oh, so you know
us already.
That'll make this easier.
I'll just tell you then.
I want this library.
Jibril:
You amigos want to take
moi library away.
My word, that's not es possible.
I would comprende.
Okay, Steph,
this is a Flugel, right,
a god‐killing warrior
just like you said?
That's what
she's supposed to be.
I must have been
as cattywampus
as a squab hit in the face
with a bean gun.
Or, wait, sorry,
pea shooter, I mean.
She corrected herself.
You remind me of
this awful comedian I saw,
so, if you're doing this
on purpose, please spare us.
Pourquoi?
I had thought it was a uniquely
avant‐garde way of speaking,
but you're saying somebody
already beat me to it?
Yeah, and they suck, too.
Jibril:
Let us return
to the matter at hand.
You said you desire
my library.
Should I assume
that means...
that you wish to challenge
me to a game, human?
Uh‐huh.
I do, actually.
How interesting.
Before the ten pledges
were put into effect,
we Flugels spent our days
collecting severed heads
off the corpses
of our victims.
However, now that murder
is forbidden,
we are satisfied with
collecting knowledge instead.
It's no exaggeration
to say the books containing
that knowledge and the places
where they are held,
are, in Flugel society,
considered to be as valuable
as one's life.
So since you're asking me
to bet my life away,
what are you offering me
in exchange?
More than 40,000 books
from another world.
( screams )
Oh, no, you didn't.
It's okay, Shiro,
in our line of work,
that's a really good sign.
For 40,000,
that's quite a prize.
Where do you keep
all these books?
Right in here.
I got them to study
for quiz games‐
dictionaries,
medical reference guides,
philosophy books.
It's chock‐full of
information from our world.
Wait, you're honestly
trying to tell me
that you came here
from another world?
Yep.
That's not possible.
Huh?
You want to
back us up here?
Oh, I, uh...
If you were going to summon
a living creature
from another world,
it would require
a massive amount of magical
energy to sustain them here.
I'm afraid that even
the Old Deus
would find such a task
extraordinarily difficult.
I don't really get it,
but proof trumps all.
Look at this. Not sure
if you can read it‐
What are you talking about?
I can speak every one
of the over 700 languages
fluently, so...
I can't read these words.
A brand‐new language?
And there are 40,000 books
full of this?
( screams )
So much knowledge
from another world!
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God!
Hey, you're drooling!
You're drooling on it!
Oh, my, excuse me. I see.
I am indeed interested in
this little thin board thingy.
And yet, I fear
I still can't trust
that you're from another world
without some sort
of proof to persuade me.
Help me out here.
What kind of proof
are you looking for?
Could you please
allow me to inspect your bodies?
Inspect our bodies?
Why would you do that?
What the hell
are you checking for anyway?
Your erogenous zones.
Oh! do it for as long
as you like,
as hard as you like,
wherever you like!
Nothing good
can come from this.
Sora, that's
rated‐R stuff.
( grunts )
Damn it, you're right. Fine!
Just leave the stupid
pants on, but listen up!
This is a give and take
situation.
You touch me,
and I get to feel you up, too!
Are you crazy?
She's not just gonna let you‐
Of course.
That'll be perfectly fine.
I'm losing my mind!
So do you not care
for how it feels
when I stroke you that way?
Uh, no, it feels
pretty okay, I suppose,
more so than
one might expect.
but, uh, how to put it?
I guess I'm just feeling
a little let down,
kind of disappointed.
Is this not one
of your erogenous zones?
I mean, no,
it isn't, not really.
but, frankly,
even if it was,
I don't think any man would be
willing to admit that, okay?
And allow me to add I was hoping
you'd touch me somewhere else,
to say the least.
But all of our power comes
from the pulsating lines
of currents called
our spirit circuits.
These lines are more
concentrated at our wings
which is why
they are so very sensitive
and also very erogenous.
( moans )
Um, you like that, baby?
What, right here, you say?
And when you touch me
like that I just...
( cries out )
What are we even doing
anymore?!
I'm just helping a girlfriend
out by stroking her soft parts.
Right, sis?
Yep, it's super healthy.
I can't believe that
I'm seeing this.
I mean, she's a god‐killing
ultimate weapon.
Jibril:
( moans )
Ahem, as far as I can tell,
there would appear
to be no spirits whatsoever
residing within your bodies.
In other words, by the standards
set in our world
you two aren't technically
even defined as life.
Flugel are like living deities
and Imanity fungus.
So what does that...
Make us?
Completely unknown!
A mystery is the most wonderful
thing in existence.
It is the wellspring from which
all new knowledge is born,
and there is nothing
quite as spectacular
as the unknown!
Uh, okay, good for you.
Guess it's safe to assume that
we've proven we're not
from your world, then?
Yes, that's right.
I assumed you were nothing more
than a feeble Imanity,
but I was mistaken.
My apologies.
I meant no offense.
Of course, I will
accept your challenge,
but I'm afraid I don't
really have much to offer you
that's worth 40,000 books
from another world.
I just want the library.
How about I bet myself
as well as everything I have.
Really?!
Seriously?!
Jackpot!
Jibril:
Is that acceptable?
Sora:
Oh, yeah, we want all
of your personal rights
as a living being.
Why, that's just excellent.
Oh, if I win,
I would like to add a clause
that states that you have
to come by the library
for tea once in a while.
I'm ever so eager to learn
more about you.
( giggles )
I have no problem
with that,
assuming you do win,
of course, but in that case,
we get a second request
if we win, right?
Yes, in the extraordinarily
unlikely event
that such a miracle occurs.
( giggles )
Jibril:
The game will be word chain,
but not your run‐of‐the‐mill
kind of word chain‐
Materialization word chain.
Oh...
Sora:
Materialization word chain?
Jibril:
Yes, the rules are simple.
Just like
a normal word chain,
if you use a word
that's already been used,
fail to answer after
30 seconds,
or can no longer continue,
then it's game over for you.
Sora:
Can words be in any language?
Jibril:
Yes, but just so you know,
imaginary things
that do not exist
won't count
as a proper answer.
And remember, we're playing
materialization word chain.
If you say something
that's here,
it will disappear.
If it's not here,
it will appear.
I'm sure you can guess
the implications.
Of course,
once the game's over
everything that happened
will be undone.
So don't hesitate
to show off your knowledge.
I got it.
Okay, Shiro,
come sit here.
We'll do this together
just like we always do.
It makes no difference.
You are completely outmatched.
Take all the help you can get
and try to stay alive.
Steph:
What? Wait,
you mean you can die?
Jibril:
You can, but only
as a consequence
of actions taken
in the game.
Your opponent cannot
directly attack you.
Okey dokey, then, folks,
You have fun.
I'll just be on my merry way‐
Here we go.
( screams )
All right,
let the game begin.
Give us your
best shot.
Would you please stop ig‐
Steph, sit, stay.
No, now I cant run away.
I've had it with this.
Steph:
It's not fair! (cries)
I will offer you
the first move.
Pick any word you like.
So let me think about this.
Okay, I'll start with...
atom bomb!
Huh?
What is this?
( gasps )
Bkuli'ans!
Jibril:
Self destructing
for your first move, hmm?
That was Bkuli'ans,
one of the highest level
sealing spells, very handy.
You were fortunate.
If I hadn't decided to be so
benevolent as to protect you,
the game would
have ended already.
Benevolent?
Oh, give me a break.
Bkuli'ans!
Sora:
I was simply testing the
waters to see what lengths
you'd be willing to go to
in order to keep
this interesting little game
of ours running.
Pretty great lengths,
it would seem.
That's right.
Now that I've busted out
the most powerful weapon
in my planet's arsenal,
I see that you won't
be so easy to dispose of.
I'm so glad we
understand each other.
The last thing I want is to
waste my time in a dull game.
Oh, don't worry,
I think I can keep these
things lively.
Spirit circuits.
Well, you certainly
got right to it.
I wanted to try out
the new phrase I learned.
What? You mad?
No, it's fine.
Not having them in me
just limits my physical
abilities a bit
and prevents me from flying,
but I still have
spirits in my body,
so I'll be able to manage.
If anything, I suppose
it just makes me a bit anxious.
Oh, like when your cell phone
can't get a wireless connection?
Cell phone? Wireless?
Do they have something to do
with that magic board
doohickey?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, back off!
if I lose,
then I'll tell you.
Sora, I think she's...
Yeah, she's really getting
into this game.
Hey, Jibril, your turn,
come on.
Oh, yes, that's right.
I'll do an easy one.
Stallions.
Steph:
Stall‐
( screams )
Okay, naughty bits.
Both: Huh?
Huh?
You cool?
( groans )
Steph:
Why do you keep doing
weird things to me?!
I'm getting a little tired
of this bleak scenery.
Let's liven things up a bit.
Beach.
Sora &amp; Shiro:
( scream )
Okay, this is
nice and all,
but it's rough on someone
who never leaves home.
My turn!
Hooter‐nub!
Oh, I get it.
Let me try this.
Bikinis.
Jibril, you don't
understand at all!
If you want to see bikinis,
you need to get rid
of the clothing first!
That's how it works!
Oh, I see,
I'm sorry I ruined it.
Too bad I can't
take it back.
Would you two
at least pretend like this
is a life or death struggle?!
Whatever.
Suitcases.
Don't you mean baggage?
Anyway,
how does squall sound?
Huh? Hey, wait.
It all worked out
in the end, Jibril!
Getting a up skirt look
at a bikini bottom
is a rare thing.
and since Steph
wasn't wearing underwear,
we don't have to worry
about an extra pair
of panties
getting in the way.
Oh, yay,
I'm so glad it worked out.
And now it'll be complete.
Ladies wear!
( screams )
Huh?
Oh?
Steph:
( sobs ) No!
( laughs )
How do you like that, sis?
No nether regions at all,
and we've still got the shoes,
knee socks and collar.
In other words, it's even
better than pure nudity.
Obviously,
suitable for all ages,
very healthy and natural,
moderately sexy,
but not like super dirty
or anything.
Hey, you know what
we should call this?
the super healthy
un‐nude beach deluxe!
Sora, Omega good job.
Give me back my clothes!
Give me back my dignity!
( screams )
Hey, Jibril, don't
you ever get hungry?
Mantle.
Oh, I'm fine.
Unlike you pathetic humans,
I don't require the intake
of organic substances.
Elooshig'o.
I see.
But you get tired,
don't you?
The sun will come up soon.
Hurry up and lose
those already.
Outer core.
( screams )
Aw, if you're all pooped
and you want to quit,
go right ahead.
I'm not going to stop you.
I've already had more fun
than I've ever expected
playing with you weaklings.
Epic clock.
( yells )
You keep calling us
weaklings and feeble.
It's really starting
to get on my nerves.
Killer creature.
Well, to a mighty Exceed
rank six like yourself,
I'm sure us folks
at the bottom of the list
must look like ants
or whatever, huh?
But you know what?
Ants are pretty strong
and there's lots of them, too.
I humbly apologize.
I hadn't considered the idea
that you Imanity
were smart enough to think
of yourselves
as anything but weak.
Well, if you think
that longevity
and strength equal power,
then you must
be even dumber than we are.
( scoffs )
You're saying I'm inferior
to Imanity?
Please, do understand
that my feelings towards you
are best described
as curiously, not respect.
So don't get too comfortable,
little ant.
I could easily squish you.
anytime I like.
Effulgent oil.
Sora:
And that's exactly
why you're weak.
You're so egocentric,
you don't even know it.
Egocentric?
Yep, I'll write it.
It means you think
you're the center of everything.
Obviously.
I know what the word means.
And what makes you think
I'm so egocentric?
You say you're curious
about the unknown,
but you're so wrapped
up in yourself,
that you can't even
appreciate it.
It's about time
I taught you a lesson.
Allow me to show you...
just how weak
you really are.
Hey, Steph,
thanks for the hard work.
If you hadn't kept
all those monsters at bay,
there's no way
we would have won.
That's a little premature.
Sorry about this, Steph.
This'll kill you,
so try to hang in there.
Wait, what?
( both roar )
Both:
Lithosphere!
Huh?
( screams )
Sora:
The lithosphere
is our planet's outer surface.
You were too busy
enjoying yourself
to see that I was slowly
dismantling this planet,
starting with its mantle,
then erasing the outer core.
Maybe you would
have caught that
if you weren't
so damn egocentric.
You failed to fear
and respect the unknown,
and that, my dear,
is what makes you weak.
Now I see.
This is why you erased
my spirit circuits.
You wanted me to fall
to my doom.
The core has an internal
temperature of 6,000 degrees
and a surface temperature
of 3,000 degrees.
Well, you're in the same
pickle I am,
so let's keep playing
and see who goes first.
You were worried about
the sun coming up, right?
Early morning halo.
( both gasp )
Oxygen gas.
( chokes )
So you want to smother
me to death now?
You'll have to
do better than that.
Let's keep
this game going.
Sonata.
Agricultural enthusiasts.
You're making this
way too easy.
Okay, still air.
Once the air comes back,
I can breathe.
( gasps )
What the...
Sora:
Yes, I was right,
Jibril doesn't know
atomic theory.
You thought
if you couldn't breathe
all you had to do
was bring back air, right?
Nope, not quite.
All I got rid of was oxygen.
The rules say if something's
there, it disappears
and if it isn't there,
it appears.
The other gases disappeared
and oxygen came back.
In other words,
at these pressures,
your body cannot absorb
this much oxygen properly,
and it becomes as good
as poison to your system.
That may be so.
but at this rate,
you're just as doomed as I am.
Ew.
Sora:
Circular breathing.
What, don't tell me
you didn't see that one coming?
This is the difference
between you and us.
Shiro, let's go.
Okay.
( both exhaling sharply )
Sora and Shiro:
Real atmosphere.
Can you feel that?
The zero pressure environment
created by the absence
of the atmosphere
will cause the air left
inside of you to expand
until you burst!
If you understood that,
then you'd know why
we exhaled the way we did.
Jibril:
Still, it is useless.
( gasps )
My voice?
( laughs )
Sound can't travel
in a vacuum,
so if you can't answer
in the next 30 seconds...
Jibril:
Then I lose.
Is that what
you're thinking?
Hmm, it's too bad
you're nothing
but a pathetic
little Imanity.
You do your race proud,
for what it's worth,
but I'm afraid
that this is the absolute
end of the road.
Do you see now?
This difference between us
is a barrier
that Imanity will never
be able to overcome.
Why, you can't even find
a way to answer me.
( grunts )
Isn't it ironic?
In the end,
you will lose as a result
of the soundless
fiery world you created.
Alas, you never stood a chance.
( gasps )
Sora:
When Coulomb's
force vanishes
and all that's left
is the nuclear force
that draws atoms together,
the result is an
astronomical phenomenon
that normally only occurs
by the gravitational collapse
of super massive planets,
a hyper nova,
an explosion capable
of destroying stars
dozens of light years away.
It has the temperature
of 50 billion degrees Celsius,
rivaling the dawn of creation.
Just try and survive
that, Flugel!
Jibril:
He's right. So he
got me after all.
Even if I die,
only a fraction
of a second earlier,
I still lose.
I see now for the first
explosion was simply a ruse
to see if he could words
his opponents didn't know.
That little demonstration
gave him
all the information he needed
to set his trap for me.
He orchestrated it so that
everything that happened
after that
was just a distraction
to keep me entertained enough
to miss his true intent.
Now that I think of it,
the game was over
after the very first move.
These otherworldly beings,
no, these Imanity,
they're a terrifying race
of creatures.
( explosion )
I died, didn't I?
Yep, welcome back.
First you degrade
the crap out of me,
then you use me as a decoy
and then just sat back
and watched me die?!
The inhumanity!
I mean, in‐Imanity!
Steph, sit and beg.
( barks )
How long is this
day anyway?
Well, I'm sure you have
a lot to complain about.
But if it weren't for you,
we would have lost.
Thanks a lot, Steph.
You're great.
( whimpers )
I was utterly defeated.
No matter how much
you tried to lure me,
in the end,
there was no way to know
I would answer
with "egocentric."
That's the kind of risk
a madman would take.
( chuckles lightly )
I am challenging God,
after all.
Could a sane
person do that?
You're going...
to do what?
Sora:
It was Tet who called us
to this world.
He wants us to challenge him,
so we'll give him a run
for his money, right?
Now then, Jibril,
since you lost,
according to the pledges,
everything you have
now belongs to us.
Oh, that's right,
those 40,000 books
in my tablet
were just bait.
Feel free to borrow it
and read them whenever
you feel like it.
You can keep using
the library, too, if you want.
Jibril:
Oh, my dear departed lord,
oh, Artosh, he who created us
but no longer draws breath,
at last I achieved
the long‐held dream.
I found those worthy
to call master.
Those who I can
serve faithfully
with every ounce
of my being.
Though born of Imanity,
they would command the Elves
and even myself,
overturning my preconceived
notion of the world.
My masters, my lords,
I, Jibril of the Flugel,
ranked six in the Exceed
member of The Council
of Wings,
henceforth offer
my very being to you.
From now on,
I will find no greater pleasure
than carrying out your will,
my dear masters.
Well, all righty,
that sounds great.
Right, Shiro?
Mm.
Welcome to the team.
Okay, guys,
I've been a dog long enough!
I mean, I'd be dead
in dog years by now.
Sora:
I used to be a gamer like you.
Then I took an
arrow in the knee.
Steph:
Stop it. Just stop.