We shan't allow you to fight
the Eastern Federation.
Do our lives
mean nothing to you?
Man:
Come out, you moron!
We know you're working
with the Federation!
( groans )
So, um, this is nice,
sitting all together like this,
but why are
we here again?
You remember what I told you
after we won yesterday.
Demand number two‐
I want you, Elf.
Fiel, I'm gonna
reserve the right
to alter your memories
as I please.
What?
If I'm not mistaken,
you need us to spy for you.
You want spies?
The reason we bet
Imanity's race piece
is because if we did it,
it would make you, Miss Kurami,
spy of the Elven Gard
come out of hiding.
and when you did,
we could beat you in a game.
You thought that
if you could somehow
give your memories
to me during the game,
you could bring me
over to your side
without using the pledges
to force me.
However, even though
I agreed to help you,
I didn't see anything
in your memories
that would lead me
to believe that
you can beat
the Eastern Federation.
Are you sure
you can do it?
I said I could,
didn't I?
Anyway, I've brought
the lot of you here
for a very
particular reason.
Before we go any further,
there's something we must do.
This next step is crucial
to us fighting together.
What is it?
This sounds bad.
Let's get intimate, yeah!
( theme song plays )
What do you mean by intimate?
I'm going to assume
you mean introductions... hmm?
( giggles )
( clears throat )
I'm Kurami Zell,
nice to meet you.
That's it?
Shiro:
Just your name?
Steph:
Don't you have
anything else to add?
Sorry, that's all
I want to say.
Um... she's 18 years old,
which is the same as me,
158 centimeters tall,
her measurements
from the top are‐
Hey, stop!
That's not fair!
And her bras
are padded.
So she's actually
a size‐
Fine, fine! Stop! I'll do it
for real, just shut up!
But it doesn't make any sense
to do my introduction
before you hear Fiel's first.
Why, hello there, everyone,
I'm Fiel Nirvalen,
and all of you except that
hideous demon over there
can feel free to simply
call me Fiel if you like.
Why, it seems you've already
become prejudiced against me.
Have I done something
to offend you, my dear?
Let's see.
I suppose it might have
a little something to do
with the hundreds of thousands
of my people slaughtered
by the hands of a
certain filthy Flugel
during the great war...
or something like that.
Defendant Jibril,
your plea?
Goodness, I don't know
what to say.
See, this is what happens
when forest creatures
learn magic.
If you dumb little animals
hadn't put an anti‐flight spell
over your city,
I never even would have
noticed you.
Your little trick brought
nothing but tragedy.
I fell out of the sky
and got a big ouchy
on my head, you know?
It's not my fault that
you all ended up dying
for putting me
in a cranky mood.
Judgment‐ the defendant
Jibril is guilty.
Oh, poop!
Okay, since we're gonna
work together,
I don't want any hard feelings.
Sora:
What could Jibril do
to help you forgive her?
Okay, I'm afraid that's a very
difficult question for me.
Hey, Fiel...
Hmm?
Kurami:
We're going to need her power
for Sora's plan to work.
Could you do it
for me, at least?
All right,
how about...
you lick my feet and say,
"please forgive me,
M'lady Fiel," and then
I'll consider pardoning you.
Huh? What's this?
You long‐eared, tree hugging
mongrels certainly are cocky
considering how pitifully weak
and easy to kill you are.
And the verdict‐
Jibril is guilty.
( yells )
What now?
I seriously have to lick this
gross little monster's hooves?
Serve your sentence.
( gasps )
Okay...
( giggles )
This is the biggest
pile of bull crap,
but if that's my master's order,
then I have to obey.
Jibril:
( flatly )
Please forgive me,
my lady Fiel.
Since you're so pathetic
I suppose I must.
Wow, that went better
than I thought.
My Master, licking this vulgar
forest turd's feet
and having to apologize
is surely the ultimate
humiliation, and yet, why?
Why, when I think that
I'm doing it
because you ordered me to
does it excite me so?
Tell me, Master...
Who is Blank
that they're capable
of doing this to a Flugel?
Steph:
Excuse me!
If we're talking about
hard feelings,
then I have my share, too.
That girl used Elven
magic to cheat against me
and I'm still super
pissed off about it!
( nasally )
It's your fault
for being a sucker.
( screams )
Upon closer inspection,
maybe he's just a bully.
Kurami:
Fiel is my childhood
best friend,
but to be specific,
she's also my owner.
All:
Huh?
The kingdom of Elven Gard
is a democracy,
but despite that fact,
they maintain a social hierarchy
and promote the control
of lower‐ranked races.
To put it bluntly,
their society revolves
around a slave system.
You mean, Kurami is‐
That's right.
Kurami:
My family has been slaves
of the Nirvalen nobility
since my
great‐grandfather's era.
I was born and raised
among Elves.
The Nirvalen is one
of the most famous families
in Elven Gard and has served
in the senate for generations,
but Fiel never seemed
to care about my position.
Fiel:
Are you hungry?
Fiel, please don't be
so nice to me anymore.
If you treat a slave
like me as a friend,
then you might
get in trouble.
Kurami:
But she did treat me
as a friend.
That doesn't bother me.
Kurami:
Of course, in public,
she can't allow herself
to show any
signs of it.
To be honest, I think
the whole idea of slavery
is rather cruel
and unnecessary.
Since the last head
of the family passed away
about a year ago,
Fiel is now their
de facto leader.
So from the perspective
of society,
our relationship has become
even more complicated.
Wait a minute, Fiel!
Does that mean you're an
acting senate member now?
And since your sort of plotting
in secret to free the slaves,
wouldn't that make you
guilty of treason?
All:
Huh?!
I know, right?!
It's like a huge deal!
Yeah, a huge deal
you were actually able
to follow all that.
Oh, my God!
I'm gonna pound you.
Are you sure you're okay
with this, Fiel?
Steph:
I mean, considering
your position,
aiding us could lead
to the destruction
of Elven Gard society
as you know it.
Oh, yes, I've already
thought this through,
and I'm okay with anything so
long as Kurami doesn't get hurt.
( sighs )
I honestly don't care
in the slightest what happens
to my family
or that kingdom
because they're a bunch
of stuck‐up pricks
who can all die
and rot in Hell.
( giggles )
Wow, Fiel, that's a bit harsh,
don't you think?
Kurami's all I care about,
and I need to keep
her very close
because she cries whenever
I'm not around.
I don't cry!
I never cried in my life.
Dude, When you lost that battle
against me for the crown...
No, no, no!
Dude, When you lost that battle
against me for the crown...
No, no, no!
...you were bawling
like a little baby.
I did nothing of the sort!
I did not cry!
I had something in my eye!
Oh dear, I was afraid
that would happen.
Don't listen to them.
I didn't cry.
Just because you've known me
since I was a baby,
doesn't mean you can treat me
like a kid forever, you know!
Kurami tries to
push herself too hard.
Fiel:
Oh, there, there.
She seems kind of more like her
nanny than her best friend.
Fiel:
Oh, there, there.
Kurami:
( crying )
Anyway, enough of this crap!
It's the Eastern
Federation we've got
to start worrying
about now, all right?
Kurami:
After their ruler,
the Shrine Priestess
came to power, they became
the third‐largest country
in the world
in less than 50 years.
No one knows how great
a threat they truly pose.
Also troubling
is their mysterious
blood‐destruction ability.
Have you thought
of some sort of plan
to deal with that?
Sora:
I'm on it.
But first, if we're gonna
fight together,
it's crucial that we be on
better terms with each other.
We need to strengthen
our bonds as friends.
And the hands down
best way to do that...
I'm not gonna take a bath
with you, so forget it.
( groans )
But how did you
figure out my plan?
Give me a break, did
that idiot seriously forget
that he gave me
all his memories?
Too bad we walked
all this way.
Kurami, it is very important
to have a good rapport
with the people you'll
be teaming up with.
Are you freaking kidding me?!
Yes, that's correct.
In the world we came from,
a land called Japan,
there was a traditional ritual
for getting to know each other‐
hanging out while naked!
I haven't used the pledges
to force your will in my favor,
thus, my only hope is
to rely on the ways
of traditional culture.
Seems to me that
all you're relying on
is worldly desires
and ulterior motives.
Jibril, please explain
our ways to the girl.
Ahem, the concept
of carousing while naked
dates to the Japanese
civil wars when‐
So as you can see because
both the ancient Romans
and the modern Japanese
shared this unique concept
of a public bath...
the comics became
an unlikely hit,
and its popularity
grew nationwide.
Do you understand
now, Kurami?
I'm not even sure what
we're talking about anymore.
Don't worry about it.
I'll just go ahead and
refuse for you, all right?
What? Uh‐
This is what Kurami
is really trying to say.
She doesn't want
to take a bath
because she's self‐conscious
about her tiny boobies.
Oh, my God!
Fiel:
Oh, it's fine, Kurami.
Don't worry, a woman's worth
is not determined by such
itty, bitty trivial things.
Fine, I'll get in the bath!
If I do that then you'll get
off my back, right?
Sora:
Yeah, baby!
( yells )
Don't we have any shampoo
that isn't so weird
and degrading to use?
( struggling )
Kurami, what were you
so worried about?
Your figure's just fine.
You wouldn't know
'cause I wear baggy clothes.
Master, did you predict
that something
like this would happen?
But of course.
Sora:
Fiel I mean, M'lady Fiel,
is the magic you're using
on Kurami an illusion
or did she actually
grow some tatas
in the last 20 minutes?
Kurami, he figured
it out.
I think it's rude to be
using magic like this
when we're supposed to be
bearing our true selves.
Oh...
But you said something
about an alteration yourself.
Sora:
How gracious of you to ask.
( clears throat )
Is it possible to
turn me into a girl?
Then I too would be able
to bond with you ladies
without worrying about‐
Hey, what are you doing?!
Why, I sure can!
Stop it!
Well, lets get cracking!
Fiel:
But it's permanent.
so I won't be able
to turn you back.
Is that okay?
Unacceptable.
Woman:
Well, they certainly seem
energetic, don't they?
And it's delightful to think
that there's still some Imanity
foolish enough to challenge us,
wouldn't you agree, Ino?
Ino:
Wholeheartedly, My Lady.
Woman:
We shall soon see how well their
brash demeanor serves them.
You two have
but one responsibility
I hope you are
well‐prepared, Izuna.
Hey, Sora!
We didn't even get
a chance to talk today.
Ugh, where the heck
did he disappear to now?
Sora? Huh?
Wow, so your strategy
is to read books in the dark?
Super awesome plan.
Honestly, this is Shiro's
area of expertise.
It's pretty beyond me.
I'm just here
to keep her company.
So in the meantime,
I'm just reviewing today's bath.
( gasps )
If you're expecting me
to get all flustered like
that Steph weirdo,
it's not gonna happen!
Sora:
Too late, You're blushing.
And you've assumed
the stance of a Steph.
You came to ask me if I think
we can win or not, didn't you?
Yes, I suppose I did.
I've reviewed
your memories closely,
and from what I've seen,
all your victories have been
extremely close calls.
Like I said earlier,
this time,
you're fighting
the Eastern Federation.
You can't rely on chance.
One misstep and you're doomed.
I don't think that you can
win the same way again.
Okay, so I'll just have
to avoid making any missteps.
Can you honestly be sure
that you won't make
a single mistake?
( laughs )
No, that's impossible.
If it were just me,
I'd screw up for sure, but, see,
Blank is a whole
different matter.
Huh?
Sora:
If I make a mistake,
Shiro pulls through.
That way, the two of us
safeguard each other.
Oh.
What's the matter?
Don't you want to be friends
with me anymore, Kurami?
That's not it at all,
but if they find out about us,
and something bad
happens to you,
then I'd never
forgive myself.
As long as we stick together,
you don't have
to worry about that.
Huh?
If I ever make a mistake,
I know that you'll
be there to help me out.
Kurami, it would be perfect
if you were always by my side,
looking out for any mistake
I might make.
Then I'd never have to worry
about losing the person I love.
( sighs )
That thing you said just now,
did you get that
from my memories?
Maybe.
Anyway, the point you're trying
to make is that I wouldn't be
doubting you so much
if I could see
your sister's memories
along with yours.
I get it.
You've really found
your wings, haven't you?
Hmm?
Hey, Shiro, they say anyone
can change their fate.
I wonder if that's true.
( gasps )
It's a little cheesy
and all,
but I think the
sentiment is nice.
You should be proud
of yourself.
Sh‐sh‐shut up!
It must be hard to have
such a talented sister.
You've got your pride
to think of.
Don't let it get
you down, Big Bro.
Get out of here already!
If you stay in Elkia too long,
people will talk.
Tomorrow's the day,
isn't it?
Huh?
I want you to know
I'll be rooting for humanity.
Of course you will.
You're human, too, you dummy.
Here he comes!
Man:
You've got some nerve, asshole!
Bastards like
you don't deserve the crown!
Man:
Let's kick his ass!
( giggles )
W‐what?
Steph:
I can't believe
we're just leaving
through the
front gate like this.
You two must be insane!
Can't you see
the people are rioting?
Sora:
Oh, I can see it.
I started it, after all.
Steph:
Uh, what do
you mean by that?
Well, looks like they made room
for us, so no worries.
Let's head off, shall we?
First stop‐
to visit Izuna's house!
Let's go!
Steph:
Why are you ignoring me?!
( crowd shouting angrily )
Welcome, we have been
expecting you.
Ino:
Now then, while the game
is being prepared,
we ask that you
please wait here.
Okay, but don't forget
to let the audience in.
You're still feeling up
to this, right, Shiro?
All green here.
And how about
you, Jibril?
I am an ultimate weapon.
How I feel has no relevance
to the situation.
Simply say the word and I will
most graciously give you my all.
( gags )
I don't feel too good.
Oh, by the way, Steph,
remember that game we played
where I threw rocks
at those birds?
Well, you still owe me
something for losing that one.
( sighs )
Hey, Jibril,
can you keep the Warbeasts
from hearing what we're talking
about for a little while?
Jibril:
Certainly.
I can surround you and Dolly
in a spirit barrier
to keep the sound
from getting out.
All righty then, Steph.
I'm going to cast
a very special spell on you.
Oh, no, I've got a
bad feeling about this.
( crowd cheering )
( crowd murmuring )
Now everyone, please take a seat
in your designated booth.
( whimpers )
Before we begin today,
allow me to review the contents
of each party's pledge.
Ino:
The Eastern Federation
bets everything it owns
on the Lucia continent.
And the kingdom of Elkia
bets its race piece.
In other words,
all the rights of Imanity,
their territory,
and everything they possess
is on the line.
The game designated
by the Eastern Federation
is between our chosen
representative
and the two rulers
of Elkia,
along with
their two attendants.
The game will be conducted
with these five players.
Should the Eastern Federation
win, as is our custom,
it will demand that all
memories regarding the contents
of this game be forgotten
by the members
of the opposing party.
This includes all
of the players
as well as all Imanity
viewing the game.
Also, the rules will not
be explained
until the game has begun.
So then, once you
hear the rules
and decide you do not
want to participate,
the match will become
null and void
and your memories
of it wiped.
Are you absolutely certain
you want to proceed?
Oh, yeah, sure,
it all sounds great.
But there are two things
I want to make clear first.
One‐ if we decide
to default,
all we lose are
the memories of the game.
If your true goal was to create
some impossible game
so that you can wipe
us clean of our memories,
you better give it up now.
Hmm...
And two‐ if we catch
you cheating during the game,
it's grounds for
an immediate loss.
Well, that's one
of the ten pledges,
so I'm sure I don't have
to remind you,
but I'll be watching.
Very well! I will interpret
that as an agreement
and ask that you
state the pledge.
All:
Aschente!
Aschente. Thank you.
Let's do this, Izuna.
( sighs )
Hmm...
I won't lose to losers.
Thank you.
Hey, there, Izuna...
Yes, what now, please?
Sora:
When's the last time you really
had fun playing a game?
Huh?
Now then, are all
of you ready to begin?
Okay, Shiro,
don't let go of my hand.
You neither.
Sora:
All right,
let's start this game up!
( whimpers )
( chuckles )
I sense the presence
of magic.
Ino:
Kurami Zell?
What's she doing here?
And there's someone else.
( laughs )
Aw, you're trying to
pretend you didn't notice.
But I saw your ears move
when you felt my magic.
Kurami:
Fiel, it doesn't
look like we'll be able
to interfere with
the game from here.
Fiel:
Yes, it's okay.
I'm aware.
What's more important
is the fact
that we're watching
in the first place.
Kurami:
Right, so the
Eastern Federation
can't use any
obvious cheats.
Sora... I hope you
know what you're doing.
Ino: So he's
sharing information
with the Elves,
then, little shit.
You think you're quite
clever, don't you, boy?
But you're nothing
more than a fool
if you think the Warbeasts
would allow you
to beat us
at our own game.
Are you sure we're really
going to be okay?
I have a feeling
we might not win this one.
Come on, Steph,
do you need me to repeat
what I told you earlier?
Don't you remember why I said
I needed to start that riot?
Could you please not answer my
question with another question?!
Sora:
I need the people
of Elkia to be angry
because I don't want
an audience who's sure
that we can win this thing.
The way it is now,
everyone is watching us
as hard as they can,
making sure we don't
lose on purpose.
As a result, it's harder
for the Eastern Federation
to use obvious cheats.
There's no more
trusted observer
than someone
who suspects you.
How very crafty
of you, master.
Sora:
I'm sure they're
gonna try to use
as many tricks as they can,
and with their Warbeast
abilities at their disposal,
we're gonna need an observant
audience to watch our backs.
Victory will depend
on how quickly we can react
to the expected
and unexpected
and how we can use both
to our advantage.
( gasps )
Uh, Jesus Christ!
Steph:
Where in the world are we?
Well, I've never seen anything
quite like this before.
It's so loud and colorful.
Master, where are you...
Oh, dear, Master,
what's wrong with you?
( weakly )
We're all doomed.
This is impossible.
Sorry, Imanity's finished.
Are you friggin' serious,
after all that smack talk?!
I'm sorry, I didn't expect it
to be set in Tokyo!
I can't do anything here!
It's our home
and we're the away team!
We can't help you, I'm sorry.
Please handle this on your own.
We can't do it.
Try to understand, I'm so sorry.
Please forgive us!
Steph:
What the hell?
Sora:
No doubt in my mind!
I believe in you, Shiro!
You can do it!