[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
SERARA, THE GIRL WE
SAVED IN SUSUKINO,
IS A MEMBER OF
MARIELLE'S GUILD,
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE.
A GUILD IS BASICALLY A TEAM
OF ADVENTURER PLAYER CHARACTERS.
GUILDS OFFER MANY ADVANTAGES
THAT PARTIES, WHICH ARE MORE
PROVISIONAL, DON'T HAVE.
FOR EXAMPLE, A SHARED
VAULT IN THE GAME'S BANK
AND A DEDICATED
COMMUNICATION SYSTEM
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
POTENTIAL USE OF A GUILD HALL
LOCATED HERE AT
THE GUILD BUILDING.
THESE HALLS CAN BE
PURCHASED OR RENTED
AND ARE DIVIDED
INTO SEVERAL RANKS.
NORMALLY YOU SELECT A HALL
BASED ON HOW MANY MEMBERS
YOU HAVE IN TOTAL.
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
USES WHAT'S KNOWN AS
A RANK "B" HALL,
CONSISTING OF 7 ROOMS.
FOR THEM, THE SIZE
IS A PERFECT FIT.
(SIZZLING)
WHILE IT'S TRUE
THAT MAKING FOOD
WITHOUT THE COMMAND MENU
MIGHT BE A LOT MORE DIFFICULT,
IT'S A LOT
MORE REWARDING.
[GHIROV]
OH, AND THE SMELL!
AND THE BURN MARKS
FROM THE PAN!
(CRYING)
IT IS SO INCREDIBLY
EDIBLE THIS TIME!
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
IT SALTY IF YOU
KEEP ON CRYING.
[SECOND] AH, IT STILL
TURNED INTO MUSH ON ME!
[NYAN‐TA]
IF YOU'RE MAKING
A COMPLICATED DISH,
YOU CAN'T EXPECT TO
DO IT RIGHT UNTIL YOUR
CHEF LEVEL IS HIGHER.
AND EVEN IF TWO PEOPLE
WITH THE SAME LEVEL USE
THE SAME INGREDIENTS,
THE DISHES CAN STILL
TASTE DIFFERENT.
IN THAT WAY, IT'S NO
DIFFERENT THAN REALITY.
[NYAN‐TA] YOU PICKING UP
WHAT I'M PUTTING DOWN?
[HIEN] SERARA IS REALLY
WORKING THE ROOM.
[ASUKA] YOU'D THINK
SHE'D BE TAKING IT EASY
SINCE WE'RE PUTTING
THIS PARTY ON FOR HER.
[NAOTSUGU] MMM.
LISTEN, KID. YOUR LEVEL
ISN'T WHAT'S IMPORTANT.
IT'S WHAT COMES
AFTER LEVELING UP.
WHAT COMES AFTER?
SPECIAL ATTACK?!
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
PANTIES ARE NEXT, DUDE!
UH, WHAT?!
[MARIELLE] LIKE, WHAT
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
[SHORYU] AH!
[NAOTSUGU] NOT MUCH.
JUST TALKING ABOUT‐
[SHORYU] NOTHING!
NOTHING AT ALL!
WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT ANYTHING! UH...
[HENRIETTA] MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE] I'M COMING.
[SHORYU] UH!
[MARIELLE]
DON'T TELL ANYONE?
[HENRIETTA] IF IT'S
AT ALL POSSIBLE,
WE SHOULDN'T
LET OUR RIVALS
LEARN ABOUT THIS
FOOD FOR A WHILE.
OH, COME ON. IT'S THE
LIFE OF THE PARTY.
AND YOU JUST MADE
MY POINT FOR ME.
[HENRIETTA] IF PEOPLE WERE
TO FIND OUT, IT COULD
CAUSE PROBLEMS FOR US.
THAT'S WHAT
SHIROE SAID.
THANK YOU FOR
YOUR HELP.
WITH SERARA, I MEAN.
[SHIROE]
UH, IT WAS NOTHING.
EVERYONE'S GLAD
TO SEE HER BACK.
LET'S DRINK
TO IT. KANPAI!
[ASUKA] HA HA HA!
[SHIROE] UH... HMM.
[HENRIETTA] AAH!
I'M SO HAPPY! OH!
NOT JUST ASHLIN
BUT AKATSUKI ALSO!
[AKATSUKI] WHAT ARE
YOU GONNA DO TO ME?
OH, ASHLIN!
[ASHLIN]
YES, MA'AM.
TODAY WE HAVE 3 TYPES
OF SUMMER DRESS FOR YOU,
ALL FROM OUR
EXCLUSIVE COLLECTION.
I AM MY LORD'S
PERSONAL NINJA!
I CAN'T WEAR SUCH
FRILLY THINGS!
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE GAVE ME HIS
PERMISSION TO PLAY WITH YOU,
SO IT'S PLAYTIME.
UH, MY LORD
SOLD ME OUT?
[AKATSUKI]
HE SOLD ME OUT!
(PEOPLE MOANING)
YES. I LOVE YOU,
TOO, MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE] HMM.
[SHIROE] HMM.
[MARIELLE] WE'LL BE BUSY
CLEANING TOMORROW.
ARE YOU HEADED
TO BED NOW?
[SHIROE] I'M NOT
REALLY THAT SLEEPY.
WELL, THEN, WOULD YOU LIKE
ME TO PUT ON SOME TEA?
[MARIELLE] YOU, LIKE, REALLY
HELPED US THIS TIME.
THANK YOU.
[SHIROE]
IT'S OK, HONESTLY.
I REALLY DIDN'T DO MUCH
OF ANYTHING THAT GREAT.
YOU SAVED SERARA
FROM A CREEPY STALKER
WHO WANTED TO KEEP HER,
SO THAT'S PRETTY BIG.
OK, SO WHAT ELSE
HAS BEEN GOING ON
WHILE WE WERE GONE?
AROUND HERE?
IN AKIHABARA?
[SHIROE] MM‐HMM.
[MARIELLE] HMM.
IT SEEMS TO BE A LITTLE
BETTER THAN IT WAS.
I THINK SO.
THERE'S NOT AS MUCH
PLAYER KILLING,
AND IT SEEMS SAFER, ANYWAY.
HERE'S THE THING.
I CAN'T PUT MY FINGER ON IT,
BUT SOMETHING SEEMS TO
HAVE EVERYONE UNEASY.
YEAH. IT'S ALMOST LIKE
PEOPLE ARE BANDING TOGETHER
INTO THEIR OWN
SOCIAL CLIQUES.
"SOCIAL CLIQUES"?
[MARIELLE]
WE'RE A SMALL GUILD
WITH FEWER THAN
30 MEMBERS, RIGHT?
WE HAVE 4 LEVEL 90s,
BUT MOST OF US ARE UNDER 50.
BUT THERE ARE SOME HUGE
GUILDS OUT THERE.
AT THE VERY LEAST, YOU'VE
HEARD OF D. D. D., HAVEN'T YOU?
THEY'RE THE GUYS
WITH KRUSTY.
[SHIROE] YEAH.
THOSE WERE THE GUYS
WHO FINALLY BEAT
ORACLE TOWER, RIGHT?
A LOT OF GUYS WERE
TALKING SMACK ABOUT
HOW A JAPANESE GUILD
WOULD NEVER BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT IT.
[MARIELLE] YEAH.
A RAID FIGHT NEEDS ABOUT 500
INDIVIDUAL PLAYER FIGHTS
TO GO OFF PROPERLY.
D. D. D. HAS NEARLY
1,500 PLAYERS
WITH MORE THAN A
HANDFUL OF LEVEL 90'S.
WELL, THAT'S
PRETTY BIG FOR
A SOCIAL CLIQUE.
IT JUST FEELS LIKE
THE BIGGER GUILDS
ARE RUNNING THIS TOWN
THROUGH SOME SORT OF
TYRANNY BY MAJORITY.
EVEN THE SHOPKEEPERS
ARE FEELING BULLIED
BY ALL THE CLIQUES.
I HAD NO IDEA.
[MARIELLE] WE'RE HAVING
THE SAME PROBLEM IN
THE HUNTING GROUNDS.
SINCE THE STRONG AND WEAK
GUILDS WERE DIVIDED,
A SMALLER GUILD WON'T APPROACH
A FERTILE HUNTING GROUND
WHEN IT'S ALREADY OCCUPIED.
[SHIROE] THEN THE LARGER
GUILDS HAVE TAKEN ALL
THE GOOD HUNTING SPOTS?
THAT'S NO GOOD.
[MARIELLE] AND IT, LIKE,
GOES WITHOUT SAYING
YOU CAN'T FIGHT IN TOWN.
BUT THE HUNTING AREAS ARE
CONSIDERED NEXT TO THE CITY,
SO YOU CAN'T FIGHT THERE.
SO, YES, THERE'S LESS
PLAYER KILLING GOING ON,
BUT IT'S STILL A HOT MESS,
AND I GUESS IT'S GETTING WORSE.
[SHIROE]
YOU FIX ONE PROBLEM,
AND ANOTHER TAKES ITS PLACE.
[MARIELLE]
YEAH. THAT'S EXACTLY,
LIKE, WHAT'S HAPPENED.
IT'S NOT JUST
THE HUNTING GROUNDS.
INVISIBLE BARRIERS ARE
BEING ERECTED EVERYWHERE.
CLIQUES BECOME PARTIES
BECOME GUILDS,
AND EVERYONE'S TRYING TO
PICK A SIDE TO STAY SAFE.
[MARIELLE] IT'S NOT LIKE YOU
CAN BLAME ANYONE FOR IT,
AND THE BIGGER GUILDS AREN'T
NECESSARILY THE BAD GUYS
IN ALL THIS, EITHER.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY
LAWS OTHER THAN NOT
FIGHTING IN THE CITY,
SO YOU DON'T NEED
A CONSCIENCE TO
LIVE HERE, I SUPPOSE.
[SHIROE] MAYBE...
BUT THAT DOESN'T
MAKE IT OK, THOUGH.
[SHIROE] ALTHOUGH SOME
PEOPLE MIGHT ACTUALLY
PREFER IT THAT WAY.
I GUESS SO.
[MARIELLE]
YOU MIGHT BE
RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
[MAN] COME ON. YOU KNOW
WHAT'LL HAPPEN TO US IF WE TRY
OPPOSING THE LARGER GUILDS.
[WOODSTOCK] OF COURSE WE DO,
AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE HOLDING
THIS MEETING IN THE FIRST PLACE.
LISTEN, WE NEED
TO WORK AS ALLIES,
OR THEY'LL
STARVE US OUT.
[MARIELLE] MANY OF THE SMALL
GUILDS HAD A MEETING RECENTLY
TO TALK ABOUT BANDING TOGETHER
INTO A JOINT COUNCIL OF SORTS.
(THUD)
[MARIELLE] IT WAS...
LESS THAN SUCCESSFUL.
EACH OF THEIR LEADERS
HAD THEIR OWN OPINION
ABOUT WHO SHOULD DO WHAT,
AND WE ENDED UP QUARRELING
OVER MINOR DIFFERENCES OF
OPINION AND SELFISH REQUESTS.
[ICHIMONJINOSUKE]
WAIT, MY FRIENDS.
PLEASE. I'M SURE THIS
WILL ALL WORK ITSELF OUT
IF WE SIT DOWN AND TALK.
IT'S A WASTE
OF TIME.
COME BACK AGAIN.
[ICHIMONJINOSUKE]
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY.
I TRULY WANTED TO HELP
THIS IDEA WORK OUT.
WHATEVER. I KNEW
IT WOULDN'T WORK.
HMM. MORE BAD NEWS.
THE GUILDS OF
THE BLACK SWORD KNIGHTS
AND THE SILVER SWORD
ARE AIMING FOR 91.
[SHIROE] 91?
RIGHT. THE HIGHEST
LEVEL YOU COULD GO WAS
ALWAYS 90, OF COURSE,
BUT THEN THE
EXPANSION CAME ALONG.
[SHIROE]
RIGHT. RIGHT.
WHEN THE DEVELOPERS ANNOUNCED
NOVASPHERE PIONEERS,
THEY SAID THE CAP LIMIT
WAS GOING UP TO 100, WASN'T IT?
[MARIELLE] AND YOU KNOW THAT,
LIKE, WELL, THE APOCALYPSE
DIDN'T JUST SEAL US IN.
IT'S KEEPING NEW
PLAYERS OUT, TOO.
[SHIROE]
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT,
AND SINCE EVERYONE'S
ALREADY PICKED
THE GUILD THEY
WANT TO BE WITH...
THE BLACK SWORD KNIGHTS
HAVE ALWAYS HAD A THING
ABOUT BEING THE BEST
FIGHTERS ON THE SERVER FARM.
[MARIELLE]
THEIR GUILD MASTER,
ISAAC, IS PROUD.
OR MAYBE HE JUST LIKES
EXCLUDING OTHERS,
BUT HE WON'T ALLOW ANYONE
UNDER 85 TO JOIN.
SO IT'S NOT LIKE
HE'S DOING WHAT KRUSTY
IS DOING WITH D. D. D.,
OPENING HIS DOORS AND
TAKING IN THE SMALL
GUILDS THAT WANT TO JOIN.
ISAAC'S APPROACH IS
A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
[SHIROE]
SO HE'S TRYING TO FIGHT
QUANTITY WITH QUALITY.
THAT SEEMS
FINE, RIGHT?
TO MAKE THEIR
LEVEL 85s BETTER,
THEY'D HAVE TO HUNT
LEVEL 85 MONSTERS AND STUFF.
[SHIROE] YEAH, BUT THIS
ISN'T A GAME ANYMORE.
SOUNDS LIKE A QUICK
TRIP TO THE CATHEDRAL.
(ROAR)
[MARIELLE] IF THEY WERE TAKING
THE NORMAL RISKS, I'D AGREE.
HUH?
THEY'RE LEVELING
UP USING EXP POTIONS.
[SHIROE] EXP POTIONS?
NOW, WAIT. WHAT ARE LEVEL 85
GUYS DOING WITH EXP POTIONS?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
EXP POTIONS...
ITEMS THAT GIVE A
PLAYER A SLIGHT INCREASE
IN THEIR ATTACK POWER,
AND FASTER HEALTH
REGENERATION AFTER INJURY.
THEY ALSO DOUBLE THE EXPERIENCE
A PLAYER EARNS IN COMBAT.
"ELDER TALES" ADMINS
CONFIGURED THE SYSTEM
TO GIVE EVERY PLAYER
UNDER LEVEL 30 ONE
EXP POTION EVERY DAY.
THE IDEA WAS TO LET NEWER
PLAYERS LEVEL UP MORE QUICKLY
AND ENJOY THE GAME MORE.
KEEP THE CUSTOMER HAPPY,
AS THEY SAY.
IT'S AN EXTORTION RING.
THERE'S A GROUP CALLED
HAMELIN OUT THERE.
AFTER THE APOCALYPSE,
THEY TARGETED THE
LOWER LEVEL PLAYERS.
THEY ENTICE UNDER‐30'S INTO
THEIR GUILD FOR THEIR POTIONS,
AND NOT JUST ONE...
EVERYONE, EVERY DAY.
[SHIROE, THINKING] IT'S ALL
GOING WRONG AROUND HERE...
THIS TOWN, THIS WORLD.
WHO'S AT FAULT?
IT ISN'T JUST ONE PERSON.
WE'VE ALL GOT A PART
IN THIS, INCLUDING ME,
AND I'M NOT REALLY
DOING ANYTHING.
I MEAN, I ONLY WENT TO SUSUKINO
TO VENT SOME OF MY FRUSTRATION
AT THE WAY THINGS ARE GOING,
AND THAT'S NOT SOLVING MUCH.
[KANAMI] LOST IN THOUGHT
AGAIN, SHIROE?
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH THINKING.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
ALREADY SMART ENOUGH,
SO JUST SOLVE THE PROBLEM.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
SERIOUSLY, WHAT
AM I GOOD FOR?
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVE
A GUILD OR ANYTHING.
I DON'T HAVE A GUILD.
WAIT.
NO.
THAT'S JUST AN EXCUSE.
[ISUZU] CAN'T SLEEP?
[MINORI] NO.
[ISUZU] YEAH. I'M TOO
TIRED TO SLEEP, TOO.
[MINORI] HMM.
OH, YEAH.
YOUR BROTHER HELPED
ME OUT DURING THE
FIGHT YESTERDAY.
HUH? TOYA DID?
HE'S A GOOD GUY...
KIND, HAPPY,
AND HE REALLY
WORKS HARD, TOO.
[MINORI] AND A LITTLE
EMPTY‐HEADED.
(ISUZU CHUCKLES)
[ISUZU] YOU TWO SEEM
TO REALLY GET ALONG.
WHEN IT WAS STILL
A GAME AROUND HERE,
YOU GUYS WOULD PAIR UP AND
ADVENTURE ON YOUR OWN, RIGHT?
YEAH.
[MINORI] TOYA WANTED...
HE WANTED TO PLAY SO MUCH.
UH!
[SHIROE, THINKING]
ALL THOSE OLD GUILDS
INVITED ME TO JOIN THEM,
BUT ALL THEY
REALLY WANTED
WAS TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF MY
VETERAN STATUS ON A SERVER FARM.
I HATED IT, AND THAT'S
WHY I DIDN'T JOIN.
I DON'T KNOW.
HAVING PEOPLE RELY ON YOU
ISN'T A BAD THING, I GUESS.
[MAN 1] I WISH
OUR GUILD MASTER
HAD A BETTER HANDLE
ON THIS SITUATION.
[MAN 2] WE'RE TOTALLY
FREAKING SCREWED, MAN.
[SHIROE, THINKING] BUT YOU GET
A BUNCH OF PEOPLE TOGETHER,
AND IT'S ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE
TO TALK THEM INTO DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
COME ON, SHIROE.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY.
IS THERE A GUILD
I COULD WORK WITH?
[NYAN‐TA] HEY, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] UH!
[NYAN‐TA] STILL HAVING
TROUBLE WITH GUILDS, MY MAN?
[SHIROE]
HEY THERE, CHIEF.
YEAH?
[SHIROE]
I'M STUMPED, CHIEF.
I‐I GUESS I JUST
DON'T GET IT.
I KEEP TELLING MYSELF OVER
AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN
ALL THE REASONS I NEVER
WANTED TO JOIN A GUILD,
AND IT SOUNDS MORE LIKE
I'M WHINING EVERY TIME.
I'LL BE THE FIRST TO
ADMIT THAT THE SYSTEM
DOESN'T ENCOURAGE GUILDS TO MAKE
WHAT I CALL "MORAL CHOICES."
AND ANYBODY WITH HALF A
CONSCIENCE WOULDN'T FAULT YOU
FOR STAYING AWAY, AND YOU KNOW
I CERTAINLY DON'T, HMM?
(SHIROE SIGHS)
'CAUSE, HEY, THE BEST ADVICE
IS NOT TO BE A PART OF ANY CLUB
THAT WOULD HAVE
YOU AS A MEMBER.
HUH?
NO MATTER HOW HARD
WE TRY, WE CAN NEVER
BE PART OF SOMETHING
THAT'S ABSOLUTELY PERFECT.
EVERY SYSTEM WILL
EVENTUALLY FALL INTO DECAY.
NOW, YOU CAN HATE THAT FACT
WITH EVERY FIBER OF YOUR BEING,
BUT YOU MIGHT AS WELL
START HATING LIFE ITSELF
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT, YOU KNOW?
[NYAN‐TA]
SHIROECHI, I KNOW
YOU KNOW THIS, HMM?
THINK ABOUT THE TEA
PARTY FOR A SECOND.
IT WAS A GREAT GROUP.
I MEAN A REALLY GREAT GROUP
OF PEOPLE TO BE WITH,
BUT LIKE ALL THOSE OTHER
SYSTEMS I WAS TALKING ABOUT,
IT'S BECAUSE WE PUT ENERGY
INTO KEEPING IT WORKING.
IF YOU EVER STUMBLE
ON A TREASURE
THAT YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO WORK FOR,
THROW IT BACK.
IT'S WORTHLESS AND NOT
WORTH YOUR TIME.
HMM...
[SHIROE, THINKING]
GUESS HE'S RIGHT.
THE TEA PARTY AND THE
CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE...
THERE WAS SOMEONE HARD AT
WORK BEHIND THE SCENES,
AND IT WASN'T ME.
[SHIROE] CHIEF, WHAT DO
YOU THINK I SHOULD DO?
DO THE MOST AMAZING
THING YOU'RE CAPABLE OF.
UH, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
AS IN STOP HOLDING
YOURSELF BACK.
AH...
YOU KNOW, SHIROE,
I'VE BEEN WATCHING
YOU LATELY, MAN.
YEAH?
AND YOU NEED TO
LIGHTEN UP, DUDE.
[SHIROE] SO BASICALLY
YOU'VE BEEN WAITING ON ME?
[NYAN‐TA]
YOU GOT IT.
[SHIROE] BOTH OF YOU
WERE WAITING FOR ME?
[NYAN‐TA]
YOU GOT IT.
AND INSTEAD OF
LOSING YOUR PATIENCE,
YOU WAITED FOR ME
TO FIGURE IT OUT,
JUST LIKE THAT?
YOU GOT IT.
(SHIROE SIGHS)
(CHIME)
(MINORI GASPS)
[MINORI] VOICE CHAT? NOW?
(GASPS)
[SHIROE]
UM, HELLO?
DO YOU...
REMEMBER ME?
IT'S SHIROE.
THIS IS MINORI, RIGHT?
[MINORI] YES.
[SHIROE] LISTEN CAREFULLY,
MINORI, OK?
COUGH ONCE
SOFTLY FOR YES.
TWICE FOR NO.
3 TIMES IF YOU WANT
TO SAY SOMETHING.
GOT IT?
[MINORI, THINKING]
OH, MY GOD.
SHIROE KNOWS.
HE KNOWS WHAT'S
HAPPENING TO US.
[SHIROE] COUGH ONCE
IF YOU UNDERSTAND.
(MINORI COUGHS ONCE)
[SHIROE] THE GUYS FROM
HAMELIN HAVE YOU, RIGHT?
(MINORI COUGHS ONCE)
[SHIROE]
AND THEY'RE FORCING YOU
TO GIVE UP YOUR
EXP POTIONS, RIGHT?
(MINORI COUGHS ONCE)
[SHIROE] ARE YOU OK?
[MINORI] UH.
(MINORI CRYING)
[SHIROE]
ARE YOU OK?
(MINORI COUGHS ONCE)
[SHIROE] REALLY?
(SNIFFLING)
(MINORI COUGHS 3 TIMES)
[SHIROE]
YOU WANT TO
SAY SOMETHING?
REMEMBER, ONLY COUGH 3 TIMES
IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL MOVE QUICKLY
SO YOU CAN TELL ME.
[MINORI] UH!
[SHIROE] FOR NOW, I'LL
TRUST THAT YOU'RE OK.
SO BELIEVE IN ME,
TOO, ALL RIGHT?
I AM GONNA COME
FOR YOU AND TOYA.
GOT IT?
(MINORI CRIES)
[NAOTSUGU]
HEY, SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD,
DON'T WORRY ME LIKE THAT.
IF YOU'RE LEAVING,
SAY SOMETHING.
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT SHE SAID.
WHAT?
(CHUCKLES)
[SHIROE, THINKING]
THAT'S RIGHT. THEY WERE WAITING,
TOO, WEREN'T THEY?
FOR ME TO DO SOMETHING.
(MARIELLE GASPS)
[SHIROE] MARIELLE,
HENRIETTA, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD HELP ME
WITH SOMETHING.
YOU NEED OUR HELP?
WE'LL DO
WHATEVER WE CAN!
YOU CAN COUNT ON IT!
[HENRIETTA] YES.
OF COURSE WE WILL.
TO SAY THAT WE OWE YOU A FAVOR
WOULD BE A HUGE UNDERSTATEMENT.
[SHORYU]
WHAT IS IT?
[SHIROE] A YOUNG BROTHER
AND SISTER ON MY FRIEND LIST
NEED SOME HELP.
THEY'RE IN A REALLY BAD
GUILD RIGHT NOW,
ALMOST KIDNAPPED, REALLY.
I WANT THEM OUT,
AND I'M WILLING
TO FIGHT FOR IT.
I UNDERSTAND,
BUT ALL WE REALLY
NEED THEM TO DO
IS LEAVE THEIR
GUILD, RIGHT?
IT SHOULD BE
SIMPLE ENOUGH.
UH, SHIROE,
WHAT GUILD ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'VE HEARD OF THEM.
THEY'RE TAKING ADVANTAGE
OF LOWER PLAYERS,
OFFERING PROTECTION IN EXCHANGE
FOR THEIR EXP POTIONS.
IT'S HAMELIN.
THAT'S THE ONE.
I BELIEVE THAT THEY'VE
OVERSTAYED THEIR WELCOME.
[SHORYU] NOW, WAIT.
ARE YOU REALLY SERIOUS?
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
DESTROYING A GUILD?!
[SHIROE] NO. I MEAN
EXACTLY WHAT I SAID.
I MEAN THEY NEED
TO MAKE A PERMANENT
DEPARTURE FROM AKIHABARA.
(MARIELLE AND HENRIETTA GULP)
[MARIELLE] NOW, SHIROE,
WE UNDERSTAND HOW YOU FEEL,
BUT WE JUST CAN'T DO SOMETHING‐
[SHIROE] I'M SORRY,
BUT PLEASE LET ME FINISH.
THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING.
HAMELIN'S ONLY
A SMALL PART
OF A MUCH BIGGER
PROBLEM AROUND HERE.
(MARIELLE AND HENRIETTA GASP)
[SHIROE] SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
TO BE HONEST,
I DON'T REALLY LIKE
THE WAY AKIHABARA
FEELS RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE LAZY, NARROW‐MINDED,
AND OUT OF TOUCH.
AND THAT'S WHY I'M GONNA
CLEAN THIS CITY UP.
(MARIELLE AND HENRIETTA GASP)
[SHIROE] AKIHABARA
IS OUR HOMETOWN,
THE LARGEST CITY ON THE SERVER,
AND IT'S FALLING APART.
EVERY HEAD HANGING LOW,
NOT KNOWING WHAT TO DO,
LIKE THEY'RE JUST WAITING
BUT NOT KNOWING WHAT
THEY'RE WAITING FOR.
IT'S JUST GRAY, DULL,
AND LIFELESS.
WE NEED TO SEIZE THIS
OPPORTUNITY BEFORE IT
GETS AWAY FROM US.
[BOTH] HMM...
[SHIROE] THERE ARE 30,000
OF US, BUT THAT ALSO MEANS
THAT THERE ARE ONLY
30,000 OF US.
WE DON'T HAVE THE LUXURY
OF POPPING IN AND OUT
OF HERE ANYMORE,
AND WE'RE VASTLY OUTNUMBERED.
WE NEED TO BE... DESPERATE.
(SHORYU GASPS)
[MARIELLE]
I DON'T KNOW.
[SHIROE] I NEED YOUR
HELP, MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE] REALLY? I‐
[SHORYU] GUILD MASTER...
[MARIELLE] HMM?
COULD WE AT LEAST HEAR
WHAT HIS PROPOSAL IS?
SHIROE ISN'T THE ONLY
ONE WHO FEELS THIS WAY.
I KNOW I'VE FELT THIS
WAY FOR A WHILE MYSELF.
WOW. SHORYU...
SO TELL US, WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING TO DO, AND HOW
ARE YOU GOING TO DO IT?
WE CAN'T PLEDGE
THE SUPPORT OF THE
CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
UNLESS WE KNOW
WHAT YOUR PLAN IS.
I'M GONNA NEED SOME
MONEY TO MAKE IT WORK‐
5 MILLION IN GOLD.
[SHORYU]
"5 MILLION IN GOLD"?!
5 MILLION?!
SHIROE, EVEN IF WE
CASHED IN ALL OUR GOODS,
CRESCENT MOON'S TREASURY
WOULD ONLY HAVE 60,000.
SERIOUSLY, SHIROE, LIKE,
WHAT'S ALL THE MONEY FOR?
THE MONEY ISN'T
THE IMPORTANT THING
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
[SHIROE]
IT'S A MEANS
TO AN END.
THE REAL PROBLEM...
THAT COMES AFTER.
I NEED EVERYONE ON BOARD
WITH THIS IDEA, MARIELLE.
CALL ME CRAZY,
BUT I THINK
MORE PEOPLE LOVE
THIS TOWN THAN DON'T.
THOSE ARE THE PEOPLE
I NEED ON BOARD.
THEY'RE THE PEOPLE THAT
ARE GONNA HELP US WIN,
AND WE CAN.
THEREFORE, I WILL
ASK YOU AGAIN.
GIVE ME YOUR ASSISTANCE.
HELP ME AND MY GUILD.
(MARIELLE AND HENRIETTA GULP)
(MARIELLE GASPS)
SHIROE, DID YOU
REALLY SAY GUILD?
YOU, LIKE, REALLY SAID
"MY GUILD," DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH.
[MARIELLE]
YOU REALLY REGISTERED?
[SHIROE] YEAH. I'M SORRY,
SINCE I KNOW YOU INVITED
ME TO JOIN YOU.
[MARIELLE] IT'S FINE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE SORRY.
THAT'S GREAT.
CONGRATULATIONS!
I KNOW IT'LL BE AWESOME.
SO YOU CREATED ONE?
YOUR OWN GUILD?
YOU, LIKE,
FINALLY HAVE A HOME?
(CRYING)
[MARIELLE] I'M SORRY
I'M SO EMOTIONAL.
[SHORYU] WHAT'S IT
CALLED, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] HM?
[SHORYU]
WHAT'S YOUR
GUILD'S NAME?
OH. YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
A NAME.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
WE BEAR THE STORY OF
THOSE WHO CHALLENGE
THE EDGE OF THE EARTH.
WE ARE...
LOG HORIZON.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
DELECTABLE SCENTS
ARE IN THE AIR.
JUICY MEAT,
CRISP, FRESH LETTUCE,
AND TOMATO WITH A
TOUCH OF SOURNESS.
THE SWEETNESS OF
LIGHTLY TOASTED BREAD
AND SMOOTH BUTTER
TOPPED OFF WITH
SPICY MUSTARD.
IT'S THE CRESCENT
BURGER.
ON SALE TODAY
FOR JUST 50 GOLD.
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.