[MINORI] OK.
MY LORD, WOULD YOU
LIKE SOME JAM?
NO! THIS IS
A HOT DOG.
OK, FINE.
NAOTSUGU, HOW ABOUT
SOME MUSTARD?
UH, THESE
ARE PANCAKES.
(AKATSUKI CHUCKLES)
I DID THAT ON PURPOSE.
WHA...?
[ISUZU] SO IT'S THE SECOND
DAY OF THE SCALE FESTIVAL.
WHAT WILL YOU BE
DOING, MINORI?
[MINORI] I'LL COME
UP WITH SOMETHING.
[TOYA] OH, IT'S
A FESTIVAL.
SO YOU'VE GOT TO MAKE THE
MOST OF IT, RIGHT, MINORI?
[MINORI] MM‐HMM.
(TOYA CHUCKLES)
I'LL BE TAKING A DOG
FOR A LITTLE WALK.
UH, WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, MISS ISUZU?
I TAKE IT YOU'LL BE FIGHTING
A PILE OF PAPERWORK AGAIN.
[SHIROE]
YEAH, PROBABLY.
[NAOTSUGU] OF COURSE, I'D LOVE
TO HELP YOU AND EVERYTHING...
(CLEARS THROAT, GULPS)
BUT I HAVE AN IMPORTANT MISSION.
[ALL BUT NAOTSUGU] "A MISSION"?
[NAOTSUGU] FOOD SAFETY
INSPECTIONS.
"FOOD SAFETY
INSPECTIONS," HUH?
(NAOTSUGU CHUCKLES)
[NAOTSUGU] DUDE, THIS SPICY
SAUCE IS FREAKING AWESOME!
(CHOMP)
WHAT SHOULD I
SAFETY INSPECT NEXT?
YOU JUST WANT TO STUFF
YOUR FACE, DON'T YOU?
WHILE CALLING IT A
FOOD SAFETY INSPECTION.
YEAH. WELCOME TO
CLASS, GENIUS.
[MERCHANT] OH, COME ON!
AT LEAST TELL ME THE RECIPE.
I PROMISE, I'LL PAY
YOU FOR IT!
[VENDOR]
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'M NOT SELLING YOU
MY SECRET RECIPE!
UNTWIST YOUR PANTIES!
WHOA, FELLAS!
I KNOW FESTIVALS HAVE
THEIR SQUABBLES,
BUT LET'S BE SOME PEACEFUL
LITTLE GANDHIS, OK?
HO HO! YEAH! SEE HOW
I HANDLED THAT?
I TOTALLY DESERVE
A TASTY TREAT.
YOU'RE A HERO...
[NAOTSUGU] WHAT'S UP, HALF PINT?
IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE IN
A GOOD MOOD. IT'S WEIRD.
[AKATSUKI]
YOU'RE IMAGINING THINGS.
AND DON'T CALL ME THAT!
(NAOTSUGU CHUCKLES)
[NAOTSUGU] SOMETHING GOOD
HAPPEN WITH SHIROE?
HUH? YOU NEED
TO BACK OFF!
I'LL CUT YOU!
(ROBOT ALARM)
SIMMER, TINY.
GOT YOU ONE, TOO!
(ROBOT DINGS)
[AKATSUKI] UH!
DON'T... YOU THINK THIS
IS A BIT RIDICULOUS?
SERIOUSLY...
[NAOTSUGU] MUSTARD AND AVOCADO
AND TOMATOES AND ONIONS!
THIS IS AWESOME!
(AKATSUKI CHOMPS)
[NAOTSUGU] OH, IT'S SHIROE.
[AKATSUKI] AH!
[NAOTSUGU] HA HA! JUST
KIDDING, SHORT STUFF!
PRETTY QUICK
REFLEXES, THOUGH.
NAOTSUGU, PREPARE TO DIE!
(ROBOT ALARM)
OH, YEAH. THAT'S RIGHT.
HERE YOU GO!
(ROBOT DINGS)
[AKATSUKI] WHAT IS THIS?
[NAOTSUGU] A STAMP CARD.
EACH STAND YOU VISIT
GIVES YOU ONE STAMP.
AND, BY THE WAY, HA!
I ONLY HAVE ONE MORE TO
GO BEFORE I'M ALL DONE!
[AKATSUKI]
WHAT, NOW?
"GET ALL THE STAMPS AND
WIN A WONDERFUL PRIZE"?
I WONDER WHAT THE
PRIZE IS GONNA BE.
I HOPE THEY'RE PURE
WHITE, SOFT, AND COTTON.
OK, HERE WE GO.
MAYBE THONG PANTIES
WOULD REALLY‐
AAH! HOLY CRAP!
YOU KNOW YOU WOULDN'T BE SO
TOUCHY IF YOU'D EAT SOMETHING!
[NAOTSUGU] HEY! WHERE'D
YOU GO, PEE‐WEE?!
[AKATSUKI] I SWEAR,
THAT FRICKIN' GUY.
[TOYA] OK, MINORI,
I'M GONNA HEAD OFF
AND GO GIVE CRESCENT
MOON A HAND.
ALL RIGHTY.
SEE YOU LATER, TOYA.
[VENDOR] AN ASSASSIN
WITH JAPANESE ACCESSORIES
WOULD BE JUST SO CUTE.
[AKATSUKI] HMM...
[MARIELLE, MUFFLED]
AN INVITATION?
[MINORI] YES. IT'S FOR
THE TWILIGHT BANQUET
WITH PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
SHOULD BE GREAT.
[MARIELLE] SUPER! YOU'RE GONNA
WANT TO GO SEE KARASHIN, THEN.
[MINORI] OK,
THANK YOU, MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE] NOT A PROBLEM.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WHY ARE YOU INSIDE THESE BOXES?
[MARIELLE] WELL, IT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE, LIKE, GOOD FOR THE SKIN.
[HENRIETTA] OH, MINORI!
[MINORI] HEY, HENRIETTA!
[HENRIETTA] HAVE YOU
SEEN MARIELLE?
THIS WHOLE THING WAS HER IDEA,
AND NOW SHE'S DISAPPEARED.
I'M SORRY.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
[AKATSUKI] TURNS OUT NAOTSUGU'S
FOOD SAFETY INSPECTION WAS
JUST A PLOY TO EAT
A BUNCH OF CRAP.
[SHIROE] SURE. AND
THE FUNNY THING IS,
WITH THAT IRON
STOMACH OF HIS,
HE WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW IF
SOMETHING WAS ACTUALLY POISONED.
I GUESS NOT.
AHEM!
(HAIRPIN TWINKLES)
SO WHAT'S ALL THIS STUFF
YOU'VE GOT GOING ON HERE?
[SHIROE] GUH! A‐AKATSUKI!
[AKATSUKI] HMM?
[SHIROE] YOU'RE KIND
OF IN THE WAY.
OH, RIGHT! I SPOKE
WITH HENRIETTA EARLIER.
AND SHE WANTED ME TO SEND
YOU OVER IF I SAW YOU.
YOU THINK YOU COULD GO SEE
WHAT IT IS SHE NEEDS?
[AKATSUKI] YES, MY LORD. HERE!
[SHIROE] UH?
WHAT'S THIS THING?
[AKATSUKI]
YOUR WONDERFUL PRIZE...
HM?
[NAOTSUGU] BINGO!
THAT'S THE LAST ONE!
THE WONDERFUL PRIZE IS
ALL MINE, MOTHER‐SCRATCHER!
[VENDOR] UH...
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
WHAT? ONLY ONE STAMP?!
NO FREAKIN' WAY!
THAT LITTLE TROLL MUST
HAVE SWITCHED THEM OUT!
I'LL GET YOU, YOU TURD!
OR I COULD ALWAYS JUST
GO EAT SOME MORE.
I AM THE SMARTEST PERSON
IN THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE!
[KARASHIN] NAH, THAT
CAN WAIT TILL LATER.
CAN YOU SEND SOME PEOPLE
OVER HERE TO HELP?
WHAT?! YOU'RE
ALL BOOKED UP, TOO?
OH, MAN. WHAT A MESS!
THINGS HAVE BEEN GOING
CRAZY AROUND HERE.
[MINORI, THINKING]
I GUESS THIS ISN'T THE
BEST TIME TO TALK TO HIM.
KARASHIN! KARASHIN!
I BROUGHT ALL THE REPORTS ON
THE SOUTH BLOCK SALES FIGURES!
NOW YOU CAN SEE HOW THE‐ AH!
(CRASH)
HUH?
(TORA AND MINORI GROAN)
[KARASHIN] UGH.
[MINORI] UM, SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
[KARASHIN] OH. YOU MUST BE THE
GIRL FROM SHIROE'S GUILD, I BET.
[MINORI] YEAH,
I'M MINORI.
UM, KARASHIN, DO YOU WANT
ME TO HELP YOU OUT HERE?
[KARASHIN] HUH?
[ISUZU] SO I NEVER HEARD...
DID THE CAKE BUFFET
GO WELL YESTERDAY?
[RUDY]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[ISUZU] MINORI'S BEEN WORKING
PRETTY HARD TO TRY TO HELP
RESTORE THE REPUTATION OF
SHIROE AND THE ROUND TABLE.
THE REPUTATION, HUH?
HE SHOULD REALLY STEP
OUTSIDE AND SHOW OFF
HIS STUFF TO THE
PEOPLE MORE, YOU KNOW?
[ISUZU] HE ALWAYS JUST
LEAVES ALL THOSE SOCIAL
KIND OF THINGS TO KRUSTY.
[RUDY] YEAH, WELL, PEOPLE
ARE GOOD AT SOME THINGS
AND NOT GOOD AT OTHER THINGS.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO SHOW THE
PEOPLE MY STUFF INSTEAD!
[DRIVER 1] NONSENSE. IF YOUR
CARRIAGE WASN'T A HUNK OF JUNK,
THIS WOULDN'T
HAVE HAPPENED.
[DRIVER 2]
EXCUSE ME?!
[ELF DRIVER] JUST GET OUT
OF THE WAY, YOU MORONS!
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH
OF PEOPLE BACK HERE!
OH , SHUT UP.
YOU'RE ONLY
BEING SUCH A JERK
BECAUSE WE'RE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[ELF DRIVER] OH, WHATEVER.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU TO GET
OUT OF THE FREAKING ROAD!
[RUDY] I GOT THIS.
[ISUZU] RUDY, NO!
[RUDY] COME NOW,
GENTLEMEN, CALM YOURSELVES!
AKIHABARA IS A PEACEFUL PLACE.
I'M SO‐ AAH! AAH!
(MARIELLE SHUDDERS)
[HENRIETTA] EXCUSE ME,
BUT YOU DO NOT HAVE TIME
FOR A REST, MARIELLE.
OH, PLEASE. YOU KNOW,
LIKE, I'M NOT CUT OUT
FOR STUPID STUFF
LIKE HARD WORK.
AND YOU KNOW EVERYONE'S
BUSY SINCE WE BROUGHT
THE BURGERS BACK.
WE NEED TO PICK UP ALL
THESE BOXES AND GET MOVING.
OH! NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO!
WHILE I'M ALL
SWEATY AND GROSS!
I GUESS I HAVE
NO CHOICE HERE.
I WANT TO TAKE
A BATH RIGHT NOW!
[HENRIETTA]
YES, IT'S ME.
SO SORRY TO INTERRUPT YOU
WHEN YOU'RE HAVING SO MUCH FUN.
[MARIELLE]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT'S RIGHT. WE DON'T
HAVE ENOUGH HANDS.
WE NEED SOME BIG, STRONG
MEN TO CARRY ALL THESE
BOXES FOR OUR SALE.
[HENRIETTA] YES! OF COURSE,
MARIELLE COULD HAVE JUST
ASKED YOU HERSELF,
BUT SHE'S BEING ALL
WEIRD AND HESITANT
AND ABSOLUTELY ADORABLE.
[MARIELLE] HM...
[MARIELLE] WAIT. WHO THE
HECK ARE YOU TALKING TO?
[HENRIETTA] SHH. I'M ON
THE PHONE, SWEETIE...
[MARIELLE] BUT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT ME!
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO
BE, LIKE, QUIET? AAH!
[HENRIETTA] OH! I'M SO
GLAD YOU'LL HELP ME!
THANKS, NAOTSUGU.
MARIELLE WILL BE VERY HAPPY
TO HEAR YOU'RE COMING OVER.
SEE YOU IN A JIFFY!
[MARIELLE] JEEZ. WHY ARE YOU,
LIKE, ALWAYS SO MEAN TO ME?
HOW IS THAT BEING
MEAN TO YOU?
I'M TRYING TO HELP
YOU OUT, YOU KNOW?
[MARIELLE] I THINK I'M
GOING TO GO TAKE A SHOWER.
[HENRIETTA]
RIGHT NOW?
DON'T WORRY. I'M NOT,
LIKE, GONNA GO RUN
AWAY OR ANYTHING.
(SNIFFS)
IT WOULD JUST BE RUDE OF ME
TO BE ALL, EW, STINKY!
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
HA HA. SHE ALWAYS KNOWS
WHAT SHE WANTS, DOESN'T SHE?
I'M A LITTLE JEALOUS.
BUT I GUESS I KNOW
WHAT I...
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I MEAN, SURE, HE'S AN
ATTRACTIVE GUY AND EVERYTHING.
BUT... AND HE'S ONLY THE
SMARTEST OF ALL THE GUYS I KNOW!
UH! OH, MY GOD. WHAT AM I DOING?
WHAT AM I THINKING?!
HELLO? EARTH
TO HENRIETTA.
(HENRIETTA SCREAMS)
[HENRIETTA] OH, MY GOD. DON'T
SNEAK UP ON ME LIKE THAT!
YOU SCARED ME TO DEATH!
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SENT FOR ME.
UH, OH, YES. YOU'RE
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
OR MAYBE...
MAYBE I SIMPLY ACT
TOO INDIFFERENT
WHEN THE TWO OF
US ARE TOGETHER.
[AKATSUKI] IS SOMETHING WRONG?
[HENRIETTA] NO! NOT AT ALL.
UH! THIS AFTERNOON,
WE WILL BE SETTING UP A STAND
TO SELL A LINE OF
LOVELY WINTER CLOTHING.
I WOULD LOVE IT IF YOU
COULD HELP OUT, AKATSUKI.
[AKATSUKI] WINTER CLOTHING?
YOU AREN'T PLANNING SOMETHING
EMBARRASSING AGAIN, ARE YOU?
[HENRIETTA] OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'LL JUST BE WORKING BEHIND
THE SCENES, OF COURSE.
[AKATSUKI] THEN IT DOESN'T
REALLY NEED TO BE ME, DOES IT?
OH, AND SHIROE WILL BE STOPPING
BY LATER TO CHECK THINGS OUT.
[AKATSUKI] UH...
FINE... I WILL
CONSIDER IT.
AAH! WHAT A POSITIVELY
STRAIGHTFORWARD PERSONALITY!
YOU'RE LIKE A PUPPY!
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, LADIES! UH...
[HENRIETTA] THIS IS
THE LIFE I LIVE!
[NAOTSUGU] WHAT HAPPENED
TO HENRIETTA'S BRAIN?
[AKATSUKI] I'M NOT QUITE SURE.
[HENRIETTA] I JUST LOVE IT!
I LOVE IT! I LOVE IT!
[ELISSA] OH, WHAT SHOULD
WE DO ABOUT FOOD?
I MEAN, I REALLY DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ADVENTURERS
AND WHAT SORT OF THINGS
THEY LIKE TO EAT.
[RAYNESHIA] ELISSA,
COULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR
AND PUT A FEW MORE
FLOWERS BY THE DOOR?
[ELISSA]
YES. UNDERSTOOD,
MY LADY.
AND I THINK THAT'LL
BASICALLY DO IT.
(RAYNESHIA SIGHS)
[KRUSTY] IT COMES WITH
3 MEALS AND A NAP.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[KRUSTY] THE DEAL. IT COMES
WITH SOME MAJOR BENEFITS.
[RAYNESHIA] HE DID IT AGAIN.
HE TRICKED ME. HONESTLY!
IT'S ALL THAT STUPID
MONSTER'S FAULT.
HE'S THE REASON
THAT I'M SO BUSY.
THAT JERK. I SHOULD REMIND
HIM WHO HAS THE POWER.
I SHOULD REMIND HIM WHO'S
THE PRINCESS HERE.
[KRUSTY] I'M ALREADY WELL
AWARE OF THAT, SO NO NEED.
[RAYNESHIA] HMM! UH, KRUSTY,
HOW DID YOU GET IN HERE?
(ELISSA CHUCKLES)
[KRUSTY] ELISSA WAS KIND
ENOUGH TO LET ME IN.
[RAYNESHIA] SO WHAT IS
IT YOU WANT EXACTLY?
[KRUSTY] WELL, I HEARD
THAT YOU WERE HERE DOING
SOME ACTUAL WORK.
SO I THOUGHT MAYBE I'D COME
AND OFFER YOU MY SYMPATHY.
(RAYNESHIA SIGHS)
WELL, THAT'S THE LEAST YOU COULD
DO SINCE IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
FROM WHAT I'VE BEEN TOLD,
THE WHOLE TWILIGHT BANQUET
THING WAS YOUR IDEA.
[RAYNESHIA] IT'S MY WAY OF
THANKING THE ADVENTURERS.
ACKNOWLEDGING ALL
THEY'VE DONE FOR US.
[KRUSTY] IT WAS A SMART
CHOICE TO USE A NUMBER
OF SMALLER TABLES
RATHER THAN A SINGLE
LARGE ONE WHERE PEOPLE
ARE SEATED BY THEIR STATUS.
ADVENTURERS AREN'T BIG FANS OF
THE NOBLE SENSE OF FORMALITY.
[RAYNESHIA] YES. I THINK I'VE
GROWN TO UNDERSTAND THAT BY NOW.
GLAD TO HEAR
IT, PRINCESS.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] I CAN'T
TELL IF THAT WAS ANOTHER ONE OF
HIS SARCASTIC COMMENTS OR NOT.
SO WHY DID HE
COME HERE ANYWAY?
WHATEVER.
(SIGH)
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
THAT MONSTER'S THINKING
IS A WASTE OF TIME.
I'LL PROBABLY NEVER
UNDERSTAND HIM.
[KARASHIN] SO ARE YOU
REALLY SURE ABOUT THIS?
THIS IS A LOT TO TAKE ON.
I MEAN, I'M SURE YOU HAVE
YOUR OWN WORK TO DO, RIGHT?
[MINORI] DON'T WORRY.
I'VE GOT SOME TIME TODAY.
SO TAKE A
LOOK AT THIS.
ALL THESE FORMS HAVE COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT SIZES AND LAYOUTS
AND EVERYTHING...LIKE THIS.
[KARASHIN] IT LOOKS LIKE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND WILL BE COMING
FROM ALL OVER THE
COUNTRYSIDE. HEH HEH.
[MINORI] AND EACH TERRITORY HAS
ITS OWN VERSION OF THE FORMS.
[KARASHIN] YEAH. IT SURE SEEMS
THAT WAY. WHAT A FRICKIN' PAIN.
[MINORI] WELL, I'LL START BY
GETTING THEM ALL ORGANIZED.
[KARASHIN] OK. SO, MINORI,
DO YOU HAVE A SUBCLASS
OF SCRIBE OR SOMETHING?
NO, MY SUBCLASS
IS APPRENTICE.
I'D... LIKE...
I'D LIKE TO ASK A QUESTION
ABOUT MAYBE CHANGING MY SKILLS.
[SHIROE] YOU WANT TO
CHANGE YOUR SUBCLASS?
[MINORI] YES. BUT I DON'T
REALLY KNOW WHAT TO PICK.
[SHIROE] HMM. ALL RIGHT.
HOW ABOUT THIS, THEN?
THERE'S A SUBCLASS,
AND IT'S CALLED "APPRENTICE."
APPRENTICE SUBCLASS?
IT'S JUST WHAT
IT SOUNDS LIKE.
IT ALLOWS YOU TO BE
SOMEONE'S APPRENTICE.
THAT WAY, YOU CAN BECOME
SOMEONE'S STUDENT AND THEN
COPY ALL THEIR SKILLS.
[MINORI]
THAT SOUNDS PERFECT!
[SHIROE] BUT THERE ARE LIMITS ON
WHICH SKILLS YOU CAN LEARN.
YOU CAN ONLY GAIN THE
SKILLS FOR YOUR LEVEL,
BUT YOU DO GET A BONUS,
SO YOU CAN LEVEL UP QUICKLY.
AND THE BEST PART IS
WHEN YOU CHANGE CLASSES,
YOU STILL KEEP YOUR
EXPERIENCE POINTS.
UNTIL YOU DECIDE
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO,
IT MIGHT NOT BE A BAD IDEA.
[MINORI] IT'S SETTLED. I HAVE
DECIDED TO BECOME AN APPRENTICE.
[SHIROE] HUH! THAT WAS FAST.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR TAILORING SKILL?
YOU STILL HAVE
THAT, DON'T YOU?
YEAH. BUT I DIDN'T
PICK THAT BECAUSE I
LIKED IT OR ANYTHING.
SO ANYWAY...
UM, SHIROE, I WOULD LIKE
YOU TO BE MY MENTOR.
UH, YOU WANT ME?
[MINORI, THINKING] I CHANGED
MY SUBCLASS FOR A REASON...
BECAUSE I WANTED TO
BE USEFUL TO SHIROE.
AND IF I CAN BE OF HELP TO
THE PEOPLE OF AKIHABARA,
THEN IT ALSO MIGHT HELP
MY MENTOR'S REPUTATION
AND EVERYONE IN
THE ROUND TABLE.
AND FOR THAT, I MUST BE
FOCUSED AND DILIGENT.
AND GROW AND MOVE ONE
STEP AT A TIME.
RIGHT NOW, THIS IS
MY BATTLEFIELD!
[KARASHIN] HOLY CRAP!
YOU ARE, LIKE,
CRAZY FAST, MINORI!
[MINORI] I'M SHIROE'S STUDENT,
AFTER ALL. HEE HEE!
[SERARA] THIS IS GREAT!
[NYANTA] THE TOMATO SAUCE
HERE IS DELIGHTFUL.
[SERARA] NOW I'LL HAVE ENOUGH
ENERGY TO GO BACK TO CRESCENT
MOON THIS AFTERNOON.
NOW, THERE'S THAT
SMILE I LOVE.
I'LL DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO HELP YOU OUT, BABY.
(SERARA CHUCKLES)
(MAN YELLS, DISHES CRASH)
[WAITRESS] OH, MY GOD.
I AM SO SORRY!
[NOBLEMAN]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?!
JUST LOOK AT THIS STAIN!
I'LL PAY FOR IT, SIR.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
[NOBLEMAN]
OH, YEAH, RIGHT!
YOU COULD NEVER
AFFORD IT! HONESTLY!
YOU SEE? THIS IS WHY I TOLD YOU
IT WASN'T WORTH COMING TO
A FILTHY PLACE LIKE THIS!
THAT'S AWFUL...
[MAN IN FUR HAT]
WHAT'S THAT DUDE'S PROBLEM?
[BLOND ELF] I THINK PRETTY
BOY'S IN THE WRONG PLACE.
[MAN WITH GLASSES]
HE SHOULD JUST GET LOST.
WHICH OF YOU PEASANTS
JUST DARED TO INSULT ME?!
[MAN IN FUR HAT]
THAT WOULD BE US.
VERY WELL, THEN,
GUESS I'LL HAVE TO TEACH YOU
BRATS A PAINFUL LESSON!
[MAN IN FUR HAT] YEAH.
[BLOND ELF]
LOOKING FOR TROUBLE,
FANCY PANTS?
[MAN WITH GLASSES]
'CAUSE YOU JUST FOUND IT.
DO SOMETHING,
NYANTA!
DON'T YOU WORRY YOUR
PRETTY LITTLE HEAD.
AH!
[NYANTA] MEOW...
[NOBLEMAN] AND WHAT
DO YOU WANT, CAT?
[NYANTA]
OH, I'M NO CAT,
GOOD SIR.
BUT I AM A PROUD MEMBER
OF THE CAT PEOPLE.
[NOBLEMAN]
YEAH, I NEVER
HEARD OF THEM. UH!
[NYANTA] GUESS IT'S TIME FOR
ME TO ILLUMINATE YOU, HMM?
[NOBLEMAN]
HEY! UNHAND ME
THIS INSTANT!
(PATRONS LAUGH)
[NOBLEMAN] LET ME GO.
LET ME GO NOW! AAH!
[KNIGHTS] MY LORD!
[NYANTA] YOU REALLY OUGHT TO
TRY MINDING YOUR MANNERS.
AKIHABARA HAS A FEW COMMON
COURTESY RULES BY WHICH
WE ALL MUST ABIDE.
[NOBLEMAN] YOU'VE DISGRACED ME,
YOU DISGUSTING ANIMAL!
[MUSTACHED KNIGHT] MY LORD,
PLEASE CONTROL YOURSELF!
[NOBLEMAN]
YOU MAKE ME SICK!
[KNIGHT WITH BLACK HAIR]
PLEASE CALM DOWN!
[NOBLEMAN] GET OFF! YOU'RE GONNA
PAY FOR THIS, I SWEAR TO YOU,
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO.
[SERARA, THINKING]
NYANTA'S SO COOL!
MEOW...
[SHIROE] A CONFLICT WITH THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND... AGAIN?
[NYANTA, VOICE‐CHAT]
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, YOU MIGHT WANT
TO BEEF UP SECURITY.
TO A DEGREE, I GUESS
I EXPECTED THIS
SINCE THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
LIVE IN A CLASS‐BASED SOCIETY
WHILE WE LIVE FREE.
[NYANTA] THAT'S TRUE.
AND ALL OF THE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND'S TRADERS AT THIS FESTIVAL
ARE PROFESSIONALS,
WHILE EVERYONE ELSE
WHO'S RUNNING A SHOP
IS MERELY AN AMATEUR.
[SHIROE] D. D. D. AND THE BLACK
SWORDS ARE READILY AVAILABLE.
AND, OF COURSE,
NAOTSUGU'S RUNNING
AROUND OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
I THINK WE CAN LEAVE
THINGS ALONE FOR NOW.
[PLAYER 1] TEAM 3 HAS RETURNED!
[PLAYER 2]
TEAM 2 HEADING OUT!
[ISAAC] RIGHT. GOOD WORK!
[REZARICK] ISAAC, SIR,
HERE'S THE LATEST REPORT.
WE ASSISTED ONE CARRIAGE
STUCK ON A SIDE ROAD,
HALTED 4 ARGUMENTS,
AND DEALT WITH 2 CLAIMS
OF OUTSTANDING PAYMENTS.
ALL INVOLVED
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
ALL RIGHT. YOU'VE GOT
TO BE TOUGH AND DRAW THE
LINE WITH THESE CLOWNS.
YOU KEEP UP THE
GOOD WORK, REZARICK.
[REZARICK] YES, SIR.
[KRUSTY] YOU KNOW,
I HONESTLY NEVER EXPECTED
SO MANY WOULD
SHOW UP.
[ISAAC] LOOKS LIKE THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
LOVE THEIR
FESTIVALS, TOO.
IN ANY CASE,
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THE VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES
WAS THE ONE WHO BROUGHT ALL
THIS BUSINESS TO AKIHABARA.
A WHILE BACK, I INVITED
HIM TO JOIN MY GUILD.
OH?
THIS WAS AFTER THE
TEA PARTY DISBANDED
AND HE WAS STILL
JUST A SOLO PLAYER.
[ISAAC] I'D SEEN HOW
WELL HE FOUGHT WHILE
HE WAS A GUEST OF OURS.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE TURNED ME DOWN.
[ISAAC] HE SAID HE DIDN'T THINK
HE WAS WORTHY OF THE OFFER.
AND SO I LOST INTEREST
AND EVENTUALLY MOVED ON.
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO
WASTE WAITING FOR PEOPLE
WHO AREN'T READY TO
FIND AND SLAY ENEMIES.
[KRUSTY] LOOKS LIKE
AFTER THE APOCALYPSE,
OUR FRIEND HAS GROWN UP...
GROWN ENOUGH TO HAVE SOME MAJOR
INFLUENCE ON THE ENTIRE CITY.
[ISAAC] AND, MAN, THAT'S
JUST WHAT I DON'T GET.
IS THE GUY A STRATEGIST OR
IS HE REALLY JUST A GAMBLER?
SOMETIMES I'M NOT EVEN
SURE IF HE FEELS DEAD
OR ALIVE IN THIS WORLD.
[KRUSTY] HONESTLY, I THINK
SHIROE IS AT HIS BEST
WHEN ALL BETS ARE OFF
AND ANYTHING GOES.
[ISAAC] "ANYTHING GOES"?
I GET THE FEELING HE'S NOT
REALLY A STRATEGIST AT ALL.
I DON'T THINK HE'S
QUITE THAT COMPLICATED.
WHEN HE HAS TO DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES,
ESPECIALLY IF THERE'S
NOTHING IN IT FOR HIM,
HE'S AS STRONG AS
ANYONE YOU'LL EVER SEE.
(GLASSES SHEEN)
SHIROE IS LIKE A CURSED SWORD.
YEAH, I GET THAT.
BUT NOW THAT CURSED SWORD
IS CURRENTLY BURIED BEHIND
A GIANT PILE OF PAPERWORK.
WHO KNOWS EXACTLY WHEN HE'LL
BE DRAWN OUT TO BATTLE NEXT?
BUT I LOOK FORWARD TO
SEEING IT WHEN IT HAPPENS.
(ISAAC LAUGHS)
[HENRIETTA] OH, AKATSUKI,
YOU LOOK FANTASTICALLY,
RIDICULOUSLY ADORABLE, SO CUTE.
[AKATSUKI] YOU DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING ABOUT ME BEING
IN A FASHION SHOW!
YOU SAID I'D BE WORKING
IN THE BACKGROUND.
[HENRIETTA] OH, MY GOD...
[HENRIETTA] OH, THAT'S
RIGHT, HONEY, YOU ARE!
THE CLOTHING IS THE
STAR OF THE SHOW.
ALL YOU REALLY HAVE
TO DO IS PUT IT ON.
(AKATSUKI GROWLS)
[MARIELLE] HERE! YOU
WEAR THIS, SHIROE!
[SHIROE] UH, YOU
CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
[AKATSUKI] THAT'LL LOOK
REALLY GOOD ON YOU, MY LORD.
[SHIROE] I'M NOT
SO SURE ABOUT THAT.
[MARIELLE] OH, MY. I HAVEN'T
SEEN THIS MANY PEOPLE IN, LIKE,
A REALLY LONG
TIME, YOU GUYS.
[CONSTANTAN] I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE HEARING ME!
[MARIELLE] HUH?
[CONSTANTAN] I TOLD YOU
I'D PAY FOR IT!
[SHIROE] HUH?
[NEMIMI] I'M SORRY,
BUT THE MONEY ISN'T
THE ISSUE, SIR.
[MINORI] HUH, WHAT?
[KARASHIN] MINORI?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
[CONSTANTAN] I'VE COME ALL
THE WAY FROM THE FAR WEST
TO BUY THIS STUFF!
[NEMIMI] I KNOW.
AND I'M REALLY SORRY,
BUT IT'S ONLY
2 ITEMS PER CUSTOMER.
DON'T YOU
REALIZE WHO I AM?
TREAT ME RIGHT, AND I CAN MAKE
YOU FAMOUS ACROSS THE LAND!
TH‐THAT'S NOT REALLY THE
KIND OF THING WE'RE AFTER.
YOU'RE NOT
MAKING SENSE!
[SHIROE] SIR, PLEASE...
I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
YOUR POINT,
BUT THESE FOLKS LIVE
BY DIFFERENT RULES.
I MUST ASK
YOU TO LEAVE.
[CONSTANTAN] WHA‐?!
MIND YOUR OWN FREAKING
BUSINESS, FOUR EYES!
NOW, BEAT IT!
IT'S TIME
YOU LEFT.
THERE ARE MANY OTHER
SHOPS TO SEE.
[CONSTANTAN] HUH! YEAH!
AND I'M NEVER COMING
BACK EITHER!
GOOD LUCK SELLING
YOUR CRAP!
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
MASTER SHIROE.
IF HE BOUGHT
EVERYTHING IN THE SHOP,
I WOULDN'T GET TO ENJOY SHARING
MY JEWELRY WITH EVERYBODY.
[SHIROE] HA HA!
NO PROBLEM WHATSOEVER.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
THAT'S STRANGE...
WHY WOULD HE BE TURNED
AWAY SO EASILY?
[MAN 1] HEY, HOW LONG DO
I HAVE TO WAIT?
[MAN 2] I AM HERE
TO DO BUSINESS.
DON'T YOU REALIZE THAT?
[MAN 3] I'M ASKING YOU
HOW MANY YOU HAVE!
[MAN 4]
JUST GIVE ME THE
REST OF THEM!
[VENDOR] WE REALLY
CAN'T DO THAT.
[MAN 4] I'M NOT GOING
UNTIL YOU SAY "YES."
[VENDOR] PLEASE STOP...
[AKATSUKI]
WHAT'S WRONG,
MY LORD?
[SHIROE] THE MOOD IS STARTING
TO GET OUT OF HAND.
YES. MORE THAN
I'D ANTICIPATED.
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
SEEM TO BE VERY IMPATIENT.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I DON'T QUITE UNDERSTAND IT.
I CAN'T GET A CLEAR
ENOUGH PICTURE.
I‐I FEEL LIKE I MUST
BE MISSING SOMETHING.
(CHIME)
[SHIROE] HUH?
[MINORI] SHIROE, IT'S MINORI.
I'VE BEEN GOING
THROUGH THE PAPERWORK,
AND SOMETHING ISN'T
QUITE RIGHT HERE.
SOME OF THE
PAPERWORK OVERLAPS,
AND SOME OF IT IS
JUST PLAIN WRONG.
[MINORI] THERE'S A WHOLE LOT OF
VERY BASIC ERRORS AND MISTAKES.
AND, WELL, MOST OF THEM
SEEM TO BE COMING FROM...
FROM THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[SHIROE] I SEE.
SO THAT'S IT.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, WHAT'LL
WE DO ABOUT THE SHOW?
[SHIROE] MINORI, DO ME A FAVOR
AND KEEP THIS LINE OPEN.
[MINORI] RIGHT!
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI, I NEED
YOU TO FIND ISAAC
AND GET AN UPDATED REPORT
ON OUR SECURITY SITUATION.
AH.
[SHIROE] IT LOOKS LIKE...
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE MAY
BE ATTACKING AKIHABARA.
[AKATSUKI] "ATTACKING"?
[HENRIETTA] AN ENEMY? BUT WHO?
[SHIROE] I'M GOING BACK TO MY
OFFICE IN THE GUILD BUILDING.
WE MIGHT HAVE AN
EMERGENCY ON OUR HANDS.
[AKATSUKI]
I UNDERSTAND.
[HENRIETTA] UH. AN ENEMY?
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I LET MY GUARD DOWN!
ALL THE SIGNS WERE RIGHT
THERE IN FRONT OF ME,
BUT I WAS CARELESS...
AND NOW... NOW THEY
HAVE THE ADVANTAGE.
(ENGINE HUMMING)
[EIJIRO] WE'LL BE ARRIVING
IN APPROXIMATELY 30 MINUTES.
PREPARE TO DISEMBARK...
LORD MARVESS.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER] THE TOWN
OF AKIHABARA IS UNDER ATTACK.
SHIROE SENSES AN ENEMY
AND TAKES ACTION.
BUT HIS GUESSWORK IS OFF,
AND HIS CALCULATIONS FAIL.
THE ROUND TABLE
FACES GRAVE DANGER.
WHAT IS THE ENEMY
REALLY AFTER?
IN THE HOUR OF GREATEST PERIL,
THE STRATEGIST SHIROE BEGINS
HIS COUNTERATTACK,
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] WE WILL
CHANGE THE WORLD.