(ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(AKATSUKI SIGHS)
[SHIROE] AH, WHAT
IS IT, AKATSUKI?
[AKATSUKI] UH, NOTHING.
IT'S JUST...
ARE YOU GOING TO GO TO
THE PARTY OR NOT, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] NO. I'M NOT A BIG
FAN OF ALL THAT DRESSING
UP AND SOCIALIZING.
KRUSTY SEEMS TO
BE ADEPT AT IT.
OH, OK.
(SIGHS)
(ORCHESTRA PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
[NOBLEMAN 1] NO, I HEAR YOU DID
A TREMENDOUS JOB. JOLLY GOOD.
[NOBLEMAN 2] I'M TOLD YOU
DEFEATED THE GOBLIN GENERAL,
AND QUITE HANDILY.
[KRUSTY] COME, NOW. IT WASN'T
JUST MY BATTLE TO WIN.
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
AND THE ADVENTURERS PLAYED
AN EQUAL PART IN THIS,
GENTLEMEN.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] AND YOU,
SIR, ARE AN INCREDIBLE LIAR.
[FEVELLE] HE'S SO
STRONG AND HANDSOME!
[APRETTA]
HE'S JUST WONDERFUL.
[RAYNESHIA] AH.
[KRUSTY] HMM? HMM?
(FEVELLE AND APRETTA SQUEAL)
(RAYNESHIA GROANS)
(CHOMPING)
[NAOTSUGU] THE FOOD HERE
IS STUPID GOOD!
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHIROE AND HIS
BUDDIES GOT TO EAT THIS STUFF
EVERY DAY DURING
THE CONFERENCES. HA!
[NYANTA] NEED I REMIND YOU,
HMM, IT IS THE MEALS
YOU TAKE WITH FRIENDS THAT TASTE
THE BEST, NAOTSUGU‐CHI.
[BOY IN VEST] WHERE'S
THE HIDE‐AND‐SEEK GENIUS?
[BOY IN JACKET] WHERE IS SHE...
[BOY IN VEST] IS SHE HERE?
[GIRL] MAYBE SHE'S JUST
HIDING AGAIN, GUYS.
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY AREN'T YOU EATING?
WE'RE A LONG WAY
FROM WIPING OUT
ALL OF THE GOBLINS.
HOW CAN WE POSSIBLY BE
CELEBRATING VICTORY?
(HIEN GRUMBLES)
[ASUKA] IT'S BEEN ABOUT
A MONTH SINCE WE PINNED
THE GOBLIN ARMY ON
THE ZANTLEAF PENINSULA.
[SHORYU] THE GOBLIN KING
IS STILL AT THEIR HEADQUARTERS
IN SEVENTH FALL.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
WE DON'T JUST GO AND
DESTROY HIM RIGHT NOW.
[NYANTA] BUILDING OUR
RELATIONSHIPS WITH THE PEOPLE OF
THE LAND ALSO TAKES PRECEDENT.
WE CAN ALL THANK SHIROE‐CHI
FOR MAKING THAT DECISION.
(HIEN SIGHS)
[NYANTA] THE ROUND TABLE
HAS NEGOTIATED AND SIGNED
BASIC TRADE AND PEACE
TREATIES WITH EASTAL'S
LEAGUE OF FREEDOM CITIES,
BUILDING A FOUNDATION
FOR HAVING AT LEAST ONE
STRONG POLITICAL ALLY.
[NAOTSUGU] THE ROUND TABLE
HAS ISSUED QUITE A FEW
GOBLIN‐FIGHTING QUESTS TO
ADVENTURERS IN AKIHABARA.
AND THAT'S KIND OF KEPT MOST
OF THE GOBLINS IN ZANTLEAF.
[ASUKA] SO BASICALLY WE'RE
DOING THIS TO REMIND EVERYONE
THAT ALL OF US ADVENTURERS
ARE BACK ON THE MARKET
AND WE'RE WILLING TO
TAKE QUESTS AGAIN.
AND IF WE DEFEAT
THEIR KING FIRST,
THEN ALL OF THE REST
OF THE GOBLINS
WILL GO OUT OF CONTROL
WITHOUT THEIR LEADER,
BECAUSE THEY'RE DUMB!
THIS IS ALL PART OF
SHIROE‐CHI'S MASTER PLAN
TO TAKE OUT THE
SEVENTH FALL, HMM?
[HIEN] I UNDERSTAND.
[ASUKA] LOOKS LIKE HE'S GOT
THIS THING REALLY PLANNED OUT,
DOESN'T HE?
[ISUZU] ARE YOU REALLY
FOR REAL ABOUT THAT?!
I MEAN, IT'D BE REALLY
AWESOME IF I COULD JOIN
YOU GUYS IN LOG HORIZON!
YEAH, IT OUGHT
TO BE FINE.
I'LL LET SHIROE KNOW
ABOUT IT, OK?
[ISUZU] OH, THANK YOU. THANK
YOU. THANK YOU. THANK YOU!
(MARIELLE LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
YOU'VE DONE SO MUCH FOR ME.
YOU'RE THE BESTEST EVER‐EST.
ALL OF US ARE
FRIENDS, RIGHT?
WE SHOULD DO WHATEVER WE
CAN TO STAY TOGETHER.
(RUDY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
ALLOW ME TO HANDLE MISS ISUZU'S
INTRODUCTION TO MY GUILD!
CERTAINLY AN OVERTURE FROM THE
MIGHTY AND HANDSOME ADVENTURER‐
[ISUZU] OK, YOUR MISTRESSNESS!
I'M SURE YOU'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
(RUDY SCREAMS)
I'LL JUST GET THIS GUY OUT
OF YOUR WAY. I'M SURE...
(TOYA LAUGHS)
[MINORI] WELL, THEY'RE
HAVING FUN. THAT'S NICE.
[RUDY] WHY? WHY? OW!
(SERARA SIGHS)
OH, SHIROE?
SHIROE, ARE YOU THERE?
[NAOTSUGU] WHY ARE YOU LOOKING
FOR HIM UNDER THE TABLE?
[NYANTA] HE CAN HIDE
BETTER THAN THAT.
[ASUKA] COME TO THINK OF IT,
I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM EITHER.
(HIEN AND SHORYU ARGUE)
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
SHIROE IS THE KEY STRATEGIST
FOR THE ARMY OF AKIHABARA.
I MEAN, HE IS ONE OF THE GUESTS
OF HONOR FOR THE BANQUET.
AND HE DOESN'T EVEN BOTHER TO
SHOW UP AND MAKE AN APPEARANCE.
NOT SURPRISING.
YEAH, THAT'S ABOUT WHAT
I EXPECT FROM SHIROE‐CHI.
[HENRIETTA] JUST BECAUSE
IT'S PREDICTABLE DOESN'T
MAKE IT RIGHT!
(AKATSUKI CLEARS THROAT)
[AKATSUKI] SO, UH,
MY LORD... I, UH‐
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE!
[SHIROE] OH, OH, CRAP.
[SHIROE] A‐AKATSUKI,
T‐TAKE CARE OF THIS FOR ME.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD?
[SHIROE] THANKS!
YOU'RE THE BEST!
[HENRIETTA] OH? AKATSUKI!
LET'S GET YOU CHANGED, SWEETIE!
YOU ARE JUST THE CUTEST THING
IN THE WHOLE FRICKIN' CASTLE!
I WANT TO GOBBLE YOU UP AND
SQUEEZE YOU FOREVER AND... HUH?
A‐AKATSUKI?
(SHIROE SIGHS)
[SHIROE] THAT WAS CLOSE.
(CHIME)
HMM? HUH?
OSHIMA? SO HOW DID THAT
ALL TURN OUT? WHAT?
IN THE WEST?
THE DEMON FESTIVAL OF SUZAKU?
OK, SO THAT'S IT.
(CROWD OOHING AND AAHING)
[PLAYER 1] SO WE WERE
JUST RIPPING UP GOBLINS
AND TOSSING THEM ASIDE!
[PLAYER 3] YOU COULD HEAR
A PHOENIX'S CALL ECHO
ACROSS THE WHOLE VALLEY!
IT WAS LIKE, KA‐POW!
[NAOTSUGU]
KIND OF SAD.
THEY DON'T REALIZE THAT THEY'LL
LOSE SOME OF THEIR MEMORIES
IF THEY DIE ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
[NYANTA] I'M SURE SHIROE WILL
FIND A WAY TO SHARE IT.
BUT RIGHT NOW, ONLY A HANDFUL OF
THE ROUND TABLE KNOW ABOUT IT.
[NOBLEMAN 1] I'D SIMPLY
LOVE IT IF YOU'D VISIT
MY TERRITORY SOMETIME.
IT WOULD BE AN
ABSOLUTE HONOR.
YOU COULD REGALE MY TROOPS WITH
SOME TALES OF YOUR VICTORIES.
[NOBLEMAN 2] NO, NO.
IF YOU VISIT ANYONE'S ARMY,
MASTER KRUSTY,
IT JUST ABSOLUTELY,
POSITIVELY HAS TO BE MINE.
[KRUSTY] HM?
[NOBLEMAN 1] MY DAUGHTER
IS SEEKING A HUSBAND.
AND I THINK YOU'D
GET ALONG WELL.
AND, MASTER KRUSTY, I CAN'T
THINK OF A BETTER MAN.
AH.
[RAYNESHIA] GRANDFATHER,
DON'T YOU THINK...?
[FEVELLE]
AND THEN? AND THEN?
[APRETTA] WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT HAPPENED?
[WOMAN] AND THEN HEROES FROM
A MYSTERIOUS WORLD FAR AWAY
SUDDENLY CAME TO OURS.
[BOY IN JACKET] WHOA!
[GIRLS] HUH?
[WOMAN] THEY WERE VERY STRONG
AND INCREDIBLY WISE.
AND THEY WERE IMMORTAL.
THEY COULD LIVE FOREVER.
[BOY IN JACKET]
WHO WERE THEY?
[BOY IN VEST]
THE PRECURSORS, RIGHT?
[APRETTA] YOU MEAN THE
IZUMO KNIGHTS, RIGHT?
[WOMAN] NO, NO. NOT
EITHER ONE OF THOSE.
IN FACT, THEY WERE FAR MORE
POWERFUL THAN THE PRECURSORS.
[FEVELLE] OH!
[WOMAN] ONE DAY, THE KING OF
THE MONSTERS APPEARED
WITH HIS ARMY OF GOBLINS.
THEY BEGAN DESTROYING
VILLAGES AND CASTLES,
EVEN GOING SO FAR AS TO RUIN
OUR FIELDS FULL OF CROPS.
BUT THE HEROES RESPONDED QUICKLY
AND DEFEATED THE MONSTERS
ONE AFTER THE NEXT.
THEY VANQUISHED THE INVADERS
THAT HAD ONCE COVERED
THE BEACHES AND
BLACKENED THE FOREST.
BUT DURING THE RAGING BATTLE,
ONE OF THESE HEROIC WARRIORS
LOST HIS LIFE AT THE HANDS
OF THE MONSTERS.
[SHIROE] HUH?
[APRETTA]
HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
[FEVELLE] I THOUGHT THEY WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE IMMORTAL.
[WOMAN] THE ONE WHO DIED WAS NOT
ONE OF THE IMMORTAL VISITORS.
HE WAS MERELY ONE OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND...
A BOY WHO LONGED TO BE A HERO.
[APRETTA]
OH, MY GOODNESS.
[WOMAN] THE HEROES DID
NOT KNOW WHAT TO DO.
THEY BEGGED THEIR MOST
POWERFUL WIZARD TO SAVE HIM.
BUT NOT EVEN THEIR WISEST
AND MOST KNOWLEDGEABLE LEADER
KNEW HOW TO RESTORE ONE OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[BOY IN VEST] KEEP GOING!
[BOY IN JACKET] YEAH!
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?!
[WOMAN] SO THE WISE WIZARD
THOUGHT AND THOUGHT,
AND HE CAME UP WITH SOMETHING.
HE CREATED AN ENTIRELY
NEW FORM OF MAGIC,
ONE THAT HAD NEVER EXISTED
IN THIS WORLD BEFORE.
HE CONJURED A MIRACLE.
(SHIROE GASPS)
[WOMAN] AND SO THE YOUNG
BOY RETURNED TO LIFE
AND BECAME A HERO.
[CHILDREN] WOAH!
[WOMAN] BUT SOON AFTER,
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO
THE WIZARD.
[CHILDREN] WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT HAPPENED?
[WOMAN] I'M AFRAID THAT'S
ALL FOR TODAY, CHILDREN.
WE'LL JUST START FROM
THERE NEXT TIME.
[CHILDREN] OH! AW...
WOW. HOW'D SHE
KNOW ALL THAT?
(WOMAN HUMMING)
(CHUCKLES)
[REGAN] OH, HELLO THERE.
I AM HONORED BY YOUR VISIT.
AND I WOULD SAY THAT
SOME CONGRATULATIONS
ARE IN ORDER, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] HMM? FOR WHAT?
THE CREATION OF A
NEW TYPE OF MAGIC.
UHH. HOW'D YOU
HEAR ABOUT THAT?
ABOUT A MONTH AGO,
I SENSED A MAGIC UNKNOWN
TO ME IN THE EAST.
AND I SAW ITS LIGHT
FILL THE SKY.
IT WAS WORLD‐CLASS MAGIC,
THE LIKES OF WHICH CAN
ALTER THE LAWS, THE FATES,
AND THE VERY EXISTENCE
OF THE WORLD.
YES, YOU ARE INDEED EVERY
BIT THE MAN I THOUGHT
YOU WERE, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] YEAH, MAYBE, I GUESS.
BUT I WOULDN'T HAVE KNOWN IT
WAS POSSIBLE WITHOUT YOU.
[REGAN] YOU HONOR ME.
INCIDENTALLY, I ALSO FELT THE
PRESENCE OF A POWERFUL MAGIC
RISING IN THE WESTERN SKY
JUST RECENTLY AS WELL.
[SHIROE] IN THE
WESTERN SKY?
[REGAN] IT WOULD SEEM TO ME
THAT SOMEONE BESIDES YOURSELF
HAS ALSO LEARNED HOW TO
CREATE A NEW FORM OF MAGIC.
I MUST ASSUME...
IT'S ONE OF THE ADVENTURERS?
(SHIROE GASPS)
[SHIROE] THE WESTERN SKY...
ADVENTURERS...
SO THAT MEANS...
IT WOULD HAVE TO
BE IN MINAMI, RIGHT?
[SHIROE VOICE‐OVER]
AKIHABARA, SHIBUYA,
MINAMI, SUSUKINO, NAKASU.
IT'D HAVE TO BE REASONABLE
TO ASSUME THAT AKIHABARA
WASN'T THE ONLY ADVENTURER CITY
TO EXPERIENCE A MAJOR CHANGE
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE.
ALMOST ALL THE
SHIBUYA ADVENTURERS
HAVE GONE TO AKIHABARA.
UNFORTUNATELY, SUSUKINO
WAS STILL IN DECAY
WITH THE GUILD OF BRIGANDIA
HOLDING DOMINION OVER
EVERYONE THERE.
EVER SINCE WE WENT AFTER SERARA,
WE'VE CONTINUED TO SEND
EXPEDITIONS TO LIBERATE
ANYONE WHO WANTS TO LEAVE.
BUT THAT STILL MEANS THERE
ARE OVER 200 ADVENTURERS
WHO CONTINUE RULING OVER
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
MINAMI'S STILL AN UNKNOWN.
[SHIROE] YAMATO WAS ONCE UNITED
AS A SINGLE KINGDOM, RIGHT?
[REGAN] YES.
[SHIROE] I READ UP ON IT
AFTER OUR FIRST MEETING.
INTERESTING.
LONG STORY SHORT,
THE UNIFIED WESTELANDE EMPIRE...
IT BASICALLY ENDED UP LOST
TO THE HISTORY BOOKS
BECAUSE OF THEIR CONSTANT
CONFLICTS WITH THE LUQUENJE
AND DEMI‐HUMANS.
THE COWEN FAMILY OF EASTAL
IS DISTANTLY RELATED.
[REGAN] THEY ARE. AND,
OF COURSE, THE HOLY EMPIRE
WESTELANDE IS AS WELL,
WHICH PRESIDES OVER THE
WESTERN PORTION OF THE COUNTRY.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
INSIDE THAT TERRITORY IS
A CITY LIKE AKIHABARA,
FULL OF ADVENTURERS, MINAMI.
HOWEVER, LIKE SUSUKINO,
ONE GUILD RULES THE CITY.
DID YOU KNOW THE DEMON FESTIVAL
OF SUZAKU GATE WAS OUT WEST?
I AM MOST CERTAINLY AWARE.
THOUGH FOR SOME REASON,
THE EASTERN NOBLES DON'T
SEEM TO HAVE NOTICED THAT YET.
[SHIROE] THEN YOU MUST ALSO KNOW
THAT THE FESTIVAL IS SIMILAR TO
THE RETURN OF THE GOBLIN KING.
THEY'RE BOTH EVENTS REGULARLY
GENERATED BY THE GAME SERVER.
[REGAN] IT APPEARS THE IZUMO
KNIGHTS WERE ALSO INVOLVED.
[SHIROE, THINKING] THE DEMON
FESTIVAL OF SUZAKU GATE...
HINTS OF MAGIC...
SOMETHING IS
HAPPENING IN MINAMI.
[HENRIETTA] HA! I FINALLY
FOUND YOU, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] AH...
AT LAST, YOUR LITTLE GAME
OF HIDE‐AND‐SEEK IS OVER.
[TOYA] SO NOW THAT
YOU'RE IN THE GUILD,
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT TRYING
TO GET OUT OF ANY OF YOUR
CLEANING DUTIES.
[RUDY] OH!
I WOULD NOT DREAM OF IT.
YOU'LL JUST HAVE TO
LEARN THE HARD WAY
WHAT THOUSANDS OF
OTHERS ALREADY KNOW...
THE DISHWASHING FOX
OF HIGH SOCIETY.
"DISHWASHING FOX"?
[TOYA] YOU DON'T MAKE MUCH
SENSE, YOU KNOW THAT?
[ISUZU] RUDY, YOU CAN'T
JUST EAT MEAT.
HAVE SOME VEGETABLES.
THEY'RE GOOD FOR YOU.
(RUNDELLHAUS GASPING)
[RUDY] COME ON, MISS
ISUZU! IT'S SUPPOSED
TO BE A PARTY.
[ISUZU] THAT DOESN'T
MEAN EAT LIKE A SLOB!
[MINORI] HUH?
[RUDY] WHY DOES IT HAVE
TO BE ALL GREEN AND GROSS?
[ISUZU] EAT IT!
[RUDY] NO!
(ELDER TALES THEME STARTS)
[ASUKA] OH! OH HEY,
I KNOW THIS SONG!
[NAOTSUGU] THIS WAS ELDER TALES'
THEME SONG WHEN IT WAS A GAME.
IT'S MY JAM.
[MARIELLE] IT, LIKE, REALLY
IS ENCHANTING MUSIC.
[HENRIETTA] YES, BUT,
WELL, NO ONE IS DANCING.
(FOOTSTEPS)
[KRUSTY] I GUESS BOTH YOUR
PEOPLE AND MINE...
[RAYNESHIA] AH.
ARE A LITTLE BIT TOO
NERVOUS FOR A SIMPLE
SPIN ON THE DANCE FLOOR.
PERHAPS SOMEONE SHOULD
TAKE THE LEAD, THEN,
TO ENSURE THIS WHOLE
AFFAIR DOESN'T DECAY
INTO A DIPLOMATIC MESS.
WE ALREADY GOT
THEM TO FIGHT.
GETTING THEM TO DANCE MIGHT
ALSO BE OUR RESPONSIBILITY.
"RESPONSIBILITY"?
(CROWD AHING)
[SERJIAD] RAYNESHIA, IT WAS
NOT EASTAL THAT ASKED
THE ADVENTURERS
FOR ASSISTANCE IN THE
DESTRUCTION OF THE GOBLINS.
IT WAS YOU, YOURSELF, MY DEAR.
[RAYNESHIA] OH! GRANDFATHER,
DON'T YOU THINK‐
EASTAL OFFERS OUR GRATITUDE
TO THE ADVENTURERS
AND EVERYONE WHO HELPED
FROM AKIHABARA.
BUT THAT IS WHERE
OUR OBLIGATIONS END.
[RAYNESHIA] I SEE.
IF I UNDERSTAND YOU
CORRECTLY, GRANDFATHER,
YOU DON'T INTEND TO COMPENSATE
THE ADVENTURERS FOR THEIR ROLE
IN KEEPING EASTAL SAFE
AND THAT I HAVE TO FIND
MY OWN MEANS OF DOING SO?
[SERJIAD] MY CITY, MAIHAMA,
WILL BE ESTABLISHING AN
EMBASSY IN AKIHABARA.
AND WE'LL NEED TO
SEND AN AMBASSADOR.
[RAYNESHIA]
NOW, WAIT...
[SERJIAD] HA HA. YOU ONCE SPOKE
TO ME OF THE POWER OF RESPECT.
THUS, I BELIEVE IT TO BE YOUR
RESPONSIBILITY TO STAY WITH THEM
AND TO OFFER OUR THANKS WHENEVER
THE OPPORTUNITY ARISES.
YOU SEE, IT'S A SIMPLE
COURTESY, IS IT NOT?
(RAYNESHIA SIGHS)
[KRUSTY] IT COMES WITH
3 MEALS AND A NAP.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[KRUSTY] THE DEAL. IT COMES
WITH SOME MAJOR BENEFITS.
[RAYNESHIA] AH.
[KRUSTY] I'M SURE THAT
YOU MUST HAVE NOTICED
WHEN YOU ARRIVED IN
TOWN YESTERDAY...
THAT MY FELLOW ADVENTURERS
AREN'T EXACTLY AS CONCERNED
WITH POMP AND CIRCUMSTANCE
AS YOUR PEOPLE.
WE DON'T HAVE A LOT
OF TEA PARTIES OR
FANCY AFFAIRS LIKE THIS.
THE LIFESTYLE'S A LITTLE BIT
MORE LAID‐BACK IN AKIHABARA.
YOU'LL HAVE PLENTY OF
TIME TO TAKE THOSE EPIC
NAPS YOU LOVE SO MUCH.
YOU WON'T EVEN HAVE
TO LEAVE THE HOUSE.
[RAYNESHIA] UM, SO THEN...
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
COULD IT REALLY BE THAT I'M
FINALLY GOING TO BE ABLE TO HAVE
MY 3 DAYS OF LAZINESS AT A TIME?
DAYS I DON'T EVEN HAVE TO BATHE?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW IF I'D
GO AS LONG AS 3 FULL DAYS.
[RAYNESHIA] UH!
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] GET OUT
OF MY HEAD, YOU UPPITY FREAK!
[RAYNESHIA] HMM.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] I'VE GOT
TO REMEMBER TO KEEP MY GUARD
UP WHEN I'M AROUND HIM.
(MUSIC ENDS, APPLAUSE)
HE'S NOTHING LESS THAN A
MONSTER THAT CAN READ MINDS.
YES, HE'S A
MIND‐READING MONSTER.
[GIRLS] SO HOT!
3 MEALS AND A NAP?
SO I CAN FINALLY RETURN TO
MY LIFE OF INDULGENCE.
IS THAT ABOUT RIGHT?
[KRUSTY] YEAH, IF YOU
CAN PULL IT OFF.
I MEAN, YOU HAVE A
KNACK FOR FINDING WAYS
TO RUIN IT FOR YOURSELF.
[RAYNESHIA] RUIN IT?
[KRUSTY] YEAH.
[RAYNESHIA] HM.
[SERARA] UH, NYANTA?
[NYANTA] WHAT'S BOTHERING YOU,
LITTLE LADY? WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[SERARA] I‐I...
I WAS THINKING...
[NYANTA] YEAH?
I'M REALLY GRATEFUL TO YOU
FOR SAVING ME IN SUSUKINO.
IT WAS REALLY NICE AND ALL.
BUT...
[SERARA] THE CRESCENT MOON
ALLIANCE HAS DONE A LOT FOR ME.
AND I... I NEED TO LOOK AFTER
ALL THE NEW PLAYERS. SO...
UM...
SO... SO I, UH, YOU KNOW, I...
[SERARA, THINKING] I WANT TO
BE WITH NYANTA, BUT...
[SERARA] UH, I...
I CAN'T STAY IN LOG HORIZON.
[NYANTA] AH. COME ON, NOW.
SILLY, YOU REALLY ARE SUCH
A GOOD GIRL. YOU KNOW THAT.
[SERARA] AH...
WOULD IT BE POSSIBLE FOR
THIS OLD KITTEN TO HAVE
A DANCE WITH YOU, HMM?
IF YOU'D BE SO KIND?
(SERARA GIGGLING)
[SERARA] OF COURSE!
[MINORI] WHY DON'T I
GET US A DRINK?
[TOYA] SURE.
[MINORI] SO WHERE'S SHIROE?
[MALE ELF] THAT SHIROE.
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT HOW
HE TRICKED THE PRINCESS
INTO JOINING THE BATTLE?
[FEMALE ELF]
MOST DEFINITELY.
I HEARD HE DRAGGED HER
ONTO THE BATTLEFIELD
AND USED HER TO MAKE DEMANDS
OF THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[MALE ELF] EVEN HIS FRIENDS
CALL HIM A VILLAIN.
[FEMALE ELF] IT'S NOT LIKE
HIS GUILD SHOULD EVEN BE
ON THE ROUND TABLE ANYWAY.
[MALE PLAYER 1] YEAH, I KNOW
GUYS LIKE THAT...
[MALE PLAYER 2] THEY SKULK
AROUND THE SHADOWS,
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
PEOPLE'S WEAKNESSES.
[AKATSUKI] YOU AREN'T
GOING, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] HMM,
I THINK I'LL PASS.
LET KRUSTY HAVE THE
LIMELIGHT THIS TIME.
PRETTY SURE I'D ONLY MAKE
EVERYONE UNCOMFORTABLE, ANNOYED,
AND ALL AWKWARD ANYWAY.
(AKATSUKI SIGHS)
[SHIROE] HM?
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S NOTHING.
IT DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE NOTHING.
(SHIROE CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(AKATSUKI GRUNTS)
[AKATSUKI] OK. WHAT'S
THAT SMIRK FOR?
[SHIROE] I'M NOT SMIRKING!
[AKATSUKI] NO, I SAW A SMIRK.
YOU WERE SMIRKING.
[SHIROE] UH, I DON'T
THINK I WAS SMIRKING.
[AKATSUKI] GRR. YES, YOU WERE.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?!
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI,
YOU'RE BEING WEIRD.
[AKATSUKI] I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST THIS TIME,
I HARDLY DID ANYTHING.
[SHIROE] HUH?
I MEAN OUTSIDE
OF THE BATTLE.
I THINK THE ONLY THING
I MANAGED TO ACCOMPLISH
WAS TO SLOW YOU DOWN.
[SHIROE] AH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I MEAN, AKATSUKI, YOU'VE BEEN
WITH ME ALL THIS TIME.
EVER SINCE WE GOT HERE,
YOU'VE BEEN MY BODYGUARD
AND GOT ME INFORMATION I NEEDED.
YOU WERE THERE WHEN
I SPOKE TO REGAN.
AND YOU HELPED ME KEEP THE
SECRET ABOUT OUR MEMORIES.
YOU EVEN WENT WITH ME WHEN
I WENT TO SAVE RUNDELLHAUS.
I COULDN'T HAVE DONE ANY
OF THIS WITHOUT YOU.
YOU ARE AS BIG A PART OF
THIS AS ANY ONE OF US.
I MEAN IT.
(AKATSUKI SIGHS)
[SHIROE, THINKING]
I'M SO TERRIBLE AT THIS.
WHY DO I HAVE SUCH A HARD
TIME SAYING "THANK YOU"?
(MUSIC BEGINS PLAYING)
[MARIELLE] OH NAOTSUGU!
HEE HEE! LET'S HIT THE FLOOR.
[NAOTSUGU] COME ON! I'M NOT
REALLY THE FANCY‐DANCY TYPE.
[SHORYU] OH, MARIELLE...
[HIEN] I'M SORRY, DUDE.
SHALL WE BOOGIE,
MISS ISUZU?
[ISUZU] HUH?!
[ISUZU] UH...
[RUDY] FOXTROT PERHAPS?
(ISUZU CHUCKLING)
(ISUZU LAUGHS)
[NYANTA] YOU'RE A PRO
AT THIS, MISS SERARA!
[SERARA] OH, THANK YOU!
[SERJIAD] WOULD YOU CARE
TO DANCE, MILADY?
[HENRIETTA] WHY, I
WOULD BE HONORED.
(SHIROE CHUCKLES)
CARE TO DANCE?
[AKATSUKI] UH, NO, MY LORD.
I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT DANCING
OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
[SHIROE] I SAW YOU PRACTICING.
[AKATSUKI] AH!
[AKATSUKI] NO.
THAT WAS... WELL...
(AKATSUKI GROANS NERVOUSLY)
MY LORD...
PLEASE DON'T LAUGH.
[SHIROE] I'M KIND OF CLUMSY
MYSELF. I WON'T LAUGH.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN
THAT DANCE BEFORE. HA HA.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, I'M
NOT SO SURE THIS IS DANCING.
[SHIROE] YEAH, I'M NOT SURE
WHAT THIS IS. HA HA!
(CHEERING)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
A FEW DAYS LATER,
THE AMBASSADOR CAME
BACK TO AKIHABARA.
AND INSTEAD OF MAKING
A GRANDIOSE ANNOUNCEMENT,
I DECIDED TO LET A FEW PEOPLE
WHISPER ABOUT OUR LOST MEMORIES.
OF COURSE, A LOT OF PEOPLE
WERE GOING TO BE SCARED.
[GIRL] YEAH, BUT YOU
ONLY LOSE PART OF THEM, RIGHT?
[MAN] I KNOW PEOPLE WHO
HAVE DIED 10 TIMES AND THEY
HAVEN'T HAD ANY PROBLEMS.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] IN THE END,
WE MANAGED TO AVOID A PANIC.
[WOMAN] THEY SAY THE ROUND TABLE
KNEW ABOUT IT BUT HID IT.
[BOY] SERIOUSLY?
[MAN] NAH. I COULD SEE
THEM DOING IT,
ESPECIALLY THAT SHIROE GUY.
[MINORI] HM...
(MINORI SIGHS)
[SHIROE] MINORI? YOU ALL RIGHT?
[MINORI] HUH?
[SHIROE] IS THERE MAYBE
SOMETHING I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
[MINORI] OH! UM, NO.
I'M FINE, REALLY.
[SHIROE] OK.
[MINORI] UH, UM...
HMM?
I'D LIKE...
I'D LIKE TO ASK A QUESTION
ABOUT MAYBE CHANGING MY SKILLS.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] AND THEN...
AUTUMN CAME.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH? A FESTIVAL?
[HENRIETTA] UH‐HUH.
AND THE COMMITTEE FOR CRAFTING
GUILDS IS READY TO GO.
AND THEY MENTIONED THEY WOULD BE
PROUDLY DISPLAYING AND SELLING
ALL THEIR NEW PRODUCTS
TO THE WORLD.
IT'S ALL THANKS
TO MARIELLE.
IT'S OCTOBER.
AND OCTOBER IS IN
THE FALL, ALL RIGHT?!
♪ WE'RE GONNA HAVE A FESTIVAL ♪
♪ COME ON, LET'S HAVE
A FESTIVAL, IT'LL BE
LIKE SO MUCH FUN ♪
[HENRIETTA] SHE REALLY
LOVES FESTIVALS.
[SHIROE] OK...
MARIELLE, UH, DIDN'T
YOU SAY THE SAME THING
ABOUT THE SUMMER
AND THE BEACH?
OH. WHEN ARE
WE GONNA DO IT?
[MARIELLE] IN 2 WEEKS.
[NAOTSUGU] WHAT?! TWO WEEKS?!
[SHIROE] CAN WE GET READY
FOR IT THAT FAST?
[MARIELLE] IT'LL BE FINE.
JUST LEAVE IT TO MARIELLE,
THE STRATEGIST.
[NAOTSUGU] DID YOU
JUST DO AIR GLASSES?
[MARIELLE] I'VE ALREADY
PLANNED IT OUT.
AND I ALREADY NAMED IT. TA‐DA!
[ALL] HUH?
[SHIROE, NAOTSUGU, AND AKATSUKI]
"THE SCALE FESTIVAL"?
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
TWO FORKS ARE OFFERED TO YOU...
TWO BITES OF CAKE ON THEM.
WHICH WILL YOU EAT,
AND WHICH WILL YOU NOT?
JEALOUS GLARES AND A
DEMON'S SPELL. SAY, "AHH."
AN ALL‐YOU‐CAN‐EAT CAKE BUFFET
IS THE YOUNG GIRLS' BATTLEFIELD
WHERE SHIROE'S REALITY
SUDDENLY EXPLODES.
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE, WEAKLY]
WE WILL... CHANGE THE WORLD.
(SHIROE GAGS)