(BEEP)
(SHRIEKING)
(PANTING)
ELECTRICAL FUZZ!
(SHRIEKS)
[SHIROE] I GOT 'EM.
VISUAL ON 7 BRIER WEASELS.
WATCH YOUR THREE, SHIROE.
[AKATSUKI] I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
(HISSING)
[NAOTSUGU] GET SOME!
(GRUNTING)
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, THESE
LITTLE NUT JOBS CAN HIT.
TIME TO CALL UP A SHIELD SMASH.
WHAT THE‐?
THESE CONTROLS SUCK!
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU,
TWO ON YOUR NINE!
(NAOTSUGU GROANS)
DUDE, THESE
THINGS STINK!
GET THE HELL OFF! UGH!
AH!
THIS'D BE EASIER
AT MY DESK.
AKATSUKI!
[AKATSUKI] NOT ANY
EASIER HERE, MY LORD.
I'M BARELY HOLDING
THEM OFF MYSELF.
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU, AKATSUKI,
FALL BACK FOR NOW!
[NAOTSUGU AND AKATSUKI] ROGER!
[NAOTSUGU] DUDE, THIS IS
SO NOT LIKE THE GAME.
BECAUSE IT'S NOT.
THIS IS... OUR NEW REALITY.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, WELL,
REALITY IS KIND OF SUCKY.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD!
[SHIROE] WAIT!
I'VE GOT A NIGHTMARE
SPHERE ON THE WAY.
OHH!
(GRUNTING)
THAT'S A TRIFFID! WHERE THE
HELL DID THAT COME FROM?!
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD!
(SHIROE GROANS)
(WIND BLOWING)
UGH?
[SHIROE] WHOA.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
ALL OF A SUDDEN, THERE I WAS.
OHH.
WHERE AM I?
I CAN SMELL MOISTURE
IN THE AIR AND SEE HOW
BRIGHT THE SUNLIGHT IS.
(WINGS FLAPPING)
AH.
OHH.
THE WHITE‐BEAM TREE.
IS THIS REALLY... AKIHABARA?
OH.
AH! WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?!
[WOMAN] IS THIS AKIHABARA?
[MAN 1] THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
[WOMAN] THIS ISN'T REAL.
[MAN 2] I NEED YOU TO
GET ME THE GM RIGHT NOW.
WHAT, ARE YOU DEAF?
LET'S GO!
[VENDOR] CALM DOWN, SON.
I JUST SELL FOOD.
WHOA!
UGH!
(GROANS)
(BEEPING)
HUH?
WHA‐? WAIT A MINUTE.
IS THIS... IS THIS THE MENU?
[SHIROE] NO, IT'S
THE STATUS SCREEN.
I WONDER, CAN I TAP IT, MAYBE?
YEAH, HA HA.
SHOW ME THE WAY OUT.
HM?
YOU'RE KIDDING. SERIOUSLY?
OH, WHAT'S THIS?
OH!
MY FRIEND LIST!
WHO'S PLAYING TODAY?
LIT UP MEANS
THEY'RE HERE, RIGHT?
EVEN TOYA AND MINORI ARE HERE.
NAOTSUGU?
VOICE CHAT.
LET'S SEE IF THE
TELEPATHIC LINK IS UP.
(RINGING)
(CHIME)
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE?
DUDE, IS THAT YOU?!
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU!
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, SHIROE!
(SHIROE PANTS)
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU!
[NAOTSUGU] HMM?
WHAT IS IT?
WELL, UH, I ACTUALLY EXPECTED
YOU TO LOOK A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
[NAOTSUGU] WELL, YOU
LOOK ABOUT RIGHT...
A SMARTY‐PANTS DORK
WEARING GLASSES.
THEY'RE HIDING A PAIR
OF CREEPY BEADY EYES.
MY CHARACTER IN THE GAME
IS SUPPOSED TO BE A HALF‐ALV.
[NAOTSUGU] MAN, CHECK IT OUT.
THIS IS, LIKE, THE FIRST
TIME I'VE LOGGED IN IN,
LIKE, TWO YEARS.
I MEAN, THIS IS SERIOUSLY
MESSED UP, SHIROE.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
HOWEVER, IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
INSIDE THE ELDER TALES WORLD.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
[SHIROE] DIDN'T THEY ADD THE
NEW EXPANSION PACK TODAY?
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, THE NOVASPHERE
PIONEERS OR SOMETHING.
[SHIROE] I CAN REMEMBER
EVERYTHING UP UNTIL THE SECOND
THEY EXECUTED THE
UPDATE,
AND THEN THE NEXT
THING I KNOW, I'M HERE.
[NAOTSUGU] ME, TOO.
IT'S DEFINITELY AKIHABARA.
I MEAN, LOOK AT IT.
I'VE SEEN IT TOO MANY
TIMES TO MISTAKE IT.
[SHIROE] YEAH, BUT...
[NAOTSUGU] SEE, THE SKY...
WELL, IT'S IN THE SKY.
[SHIROE] YEAH.
THESE AREN'T PIXELS.
I CAN REALLY FEEL IT.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH...
[SHIROE] WE DON'T
SEEM TO BE DREAMING.
SO WE'RE STUCK IN
OUR FAVORITE MMO?
WHAT A BUNCH OF
FANTASY NOVEL CRAP.
OK, SO HOW DO WE FIND
OUR WAY BACK HOME?
[SHIROE] I HAVE NO IDEA.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW WE
GOT HERE TO BEGIN WITH.
[NAOTSUGU] OK...
SO THERE'S NO WAY TO KNOW
HOW TO GET BACK OUT,
AND THAT MEANS...
HMM?
[SHIROE] WE SHOULD
PROBABLY TREAT THIS LIKE
IT'S HOME FOR A WHILE.
[NAOTSUGU]
AND HOW DO
WE DO THAT?
[SHIROE]
DON'T TREAT IT
LIKE A GAME.
WE MAY KNOW HOW TO
PLAY IN THIS WORLD,
BUT WE DON'T KNOW
HOW TO LIVE IN IT.
[NAOTSUGU] SOUNDS GOOD.
GLAD YOU'RE KEEPING YOUR
HEAD STRAIGHT IN ALL THIS...
BETTER THAN ME ANYWAY.
SO WHAT'S THE BIG PLAN?
I KNOW YOU'VE GOT ONE.
[SHIROE] NAH, I WOULDN'T EXACTLY
SAY I HAVE A PLAN YET.
I KNOW THIS ISN'T
WHAT YOU EXPECTED,
BUT WELCOME BACK TO
THE ELDER TALES, NAOTSUGU.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH!
GLAD TO BE HERE.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
BUILDINGS AND ROADS
LOOK THE SAME.
NOT A LOT OF SURPRISES
THERE, I GUESS.
LOOKS LIKE I CAN
USE MY ITEMS,
AND MY SKILLS AND
MAGIC ARE USABLE.
[NAOTSUGU] SO HAVE YOU
TRIED TO LOG OUT YET?
[SHIROE] YEAH.
DIDN'T WORK.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[NAOTSUGU] WANT TO SEE WHAT
IT'S LIKE IN THE OUTSIDE ZONE?
[SHIROE] NO.
LET'S HOLD OFF ON
THAT FOR NOW.
HUH? OH.
[MAN 1] IT'S GOT
MONSTERS OUT THERE.
[SHIROE] HMM?
[WOMAN] GIVE ME A BREAK.
[MAN 2] NO, SERIOUSLY,
GO CHECK IT OUT.
[MAN 3] YOUR FUNERAL, MAN.
[MAN 4] SHUT UP!
[WOMAN] HELP ME!
SOMEONE HELP ME!
[SHIROE] SO YOU MADE IT BACK.
I GUESS THINGS ARE BACK
TO NORMAL AT WORK?
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, BUT SADLY,
THE BOSS DIDN'T GET ANY NEW
CUTE OFFICE HOTTIES FOR ME
TO LOOK AT, THOUGH.
[SHIROE] (LAUGHS)
MAN, IS THAT EVEN A PROBLEM?
[NAOTSUGU] COME ON, DUDE!
I GOT TO HAVE SOMETHING
TO DISTRACT ME FROM WORK.
[SHIROE] IS THAT ALL
YOU THINK ABOUT?
TWO TYPES OF MEN IN
THIS WORLD, FOUR‐EYES!
REAL MEN WHO DIG ON
THE LOVELY LADY FOLK,
AND GENTLEMEN, LIKE YOU,
TOO SCARED TO ADMIT IT!
I LOVE THE LADIES, AND
PANTIES ARE MY TREASURE!
YOU'RE THE SECOND
KIND OF GUY.
[SHIROE] THANKS
FOR YOUR ANALYSIS.
[NAOTSUGU]
WHATEVER, DUDE.
ADMITTING YOUR PROBLEM
IS THE FIRST STEP‐
[SHIROE] OH!
[NAOTSUGU]
WOAH! ARE YOU OK?
[SHIROE] UH, YEP.
BUT I'VE BEEN WONDERING,
NAOTSUGU, HOW TALL ARE YOU?
I USE THE SAME HEIGHT
WHEN I ASSIGN FOR THE...
I JUST REMEMBER, I MADE
MY CHARACTER TALLER
THAN I REALLY AM.
I GUESS THAT'S WHY
I'M FEELING A LITTLE
BIT AWKWARD IN THIS BODY.
(ROCK BOUNCES)
SHOULDN'T WANT MORE
THAN YOU ALREADY HAVE.
THAT MIGHT BE TRUE, BUT
THERE'S STILL A LOT OF OUR
TRUE SELVES IN OUR AVATARS.
[NAOTSUGU] UH... WHOA!
UH, WHAT THE HELL
IS YOUR DAMAGE, MAN?!
WHAT IF YOU HIT US?!
YOU WANT A PUNCH
IN THE PETER?!
[SHIROE]
YOU'RE... AKATSUKI!
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT, YOU KNOW HIM?
WE'VE BEEN IN A COUPLE OF
RAIDING PARTIES TOGETHER BEFORE.
I'VE NEVER HEARD HIM SAY
A THING, BUT HE'S GREAT
AT WHAT HE DOES.
[SHIROE]
TOP‐NOTCH ASSASSIN.
[SHIROE] WELL, WELL. IT LOOKS
LIKE YOU GOT STUCK HERE
WITH US, AKATSUKI.
[NAOTSUGU]
I'M NAOTSUGU, A GUARDIAN.
I'VE GOT A THING FOR
THE LADIES AND I'M NOT
ASHAMED TO ADMIT IT.
[SHIROE SIGHS]
[SHIROE]
ONE CHANCE TO MAKE
A FIRST IMPRESSION...
[NAOTSUGU]
HELL, YEAH.
[AKATSUKI] [FEMALE VOICE]
SIR SHIROE, I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR YOU.
[SHIROE] HUH?
[AKATSUKI] I NEED YOUR HELP.
I NEED SOMETHING TO FIX
THIS BODY I'M IN.
SELL ME A POTION.
[NAOTSUGU]
UH, YOU SOUND LIKE A...
[SHIROE]
WHOA. ALL THIS TIME...
YOU WEREN'T A DUDE?
[SHIROE] GUESS THAT'S WHY
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN SO QUIET.
[NAOTSUGU] IT'S A
REAL METAMORPHIC.
THOSE WERE ONLY AVAILABLE
WHEN THE GAME FIRST STARTED.
[AKATSUKI] I REMEMBERED
SIR SHIROE GOT ONE.
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, LET GO OF ME!
[SHIROE] I THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T
USE THE VOICE CHAT TO FEEL MORE
LIKE AN ACTUAL ASSASSIN.
(GRUNT)
UH, YOU DOING OK?
[AKATSUKI] AAH!
[SHIROE AND NAOTSUGU] OHH!
(BONES BREAKING)
(AKATSUKI SCREAMS)
[NAOTSUGU] UHH...
[AKATSUKI]
MUCH BETTER, THANK YOU.
(STAMMERING)
[NAOTSUGU] OH, YEAH!
'SUP, GIRL!
BABE CITY, SERIOUSLY!
YOU'VE TRULY
SAVED ME.
I APPRECIATE IT.
[SHIROE] HEY, NOW,
NOTHING TO IT.
(NAOTSUGU STAMMERS)
[NAOTSUGU] LET'S GET BACK
TO WHAT I SAID EARLIER.
CHICKS ARE AWESOME, AND
A REAL MAN AIN'T AFRAID
TO TELL THEM
ALL ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, SERIOUSLY.
YOU GOT TO BE
A MAN, MAN!
[AKATSUKI] SIR SHIROE,
YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW WHAT'S
WRONG WITH THAT GUY?
THE LIST OF THINGS IS
RATHER LONG AND VARIED.
[NAOTSUGU] YOUR FACE
IS LONG AND VARIED!
[AKATSUKI] SO WE AGREE
THAT HE HAS SOME SORT
OF MENTAL PROBLEM?
[SHIROE] UH, AKATSUKI,
DID YOU TAKE THAT POTION
TO MAKE YOURSELF CLOSER
TO YOUR REAL SIZE?
YES.
[NAOTSUGU] YOU SHOULD'VE STAYED
THAT SIZE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
[AKATSUKI] UH, THAT'S KIND
OF THE POINT OF BEING IN
A ROLE‐PLAYING GAME...
TO BE SOMEONE ELSE.
BUT BEING IN A MAN'S BODY
IN THE MIDDLE OF THIS MESS
WASN'T HELPFUL AT ALL.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
RIGHT, LIKE
USING THE CAN.
(SLAM)
(NAOTSUGU WAILS)
[AKATSUKI] UM, OK. IS IT ALL
RIGHT IF I KNEE MR. PERVY PANTS
IN HIS STUPID FACE?
[NAOTSUGU] ASK BEFORE
YOU DO IT, PIPSQUEAK!
(SHIROE GROANS)
[AKATSUKI] DO NOT
CALL ME PIPSQUEAK!
NOW, THEN, WHAT DO I
OWE YOU FOR THIS SPELL?
UH, WELL, I‐I WAS
JUST HAPPY TO HELP OUT.
[AKATSUKI]
I CANNOT ALLOW THAT.
I DON'T WANT
ANYONE TO CLAIM
THAT I'M UNGRATEFUL.
NO, IT'S OK. REALLY.
OR IF YOU WANT,
YOU CAN LET ME GET
A COUPLE OF HANDFUL‐
(SLAM)
(NAOTSUGU WAILS)
(THUD)
SIR SHIROE, IS IT ALL
RIGHT IF I KNEE THIS LOSER
IN HIS STUPID
FACE AGAIN?
[NAOTSUGU] I SAID TO ASK BEFORE
YOU DO IT, LITTLE BIT!
YOU DIDN'T EVEN LET ME
FINISH MY SENTENCE!
YOU WERE OBVIOUSLY GONNA
SAY SOMETHING GROSS.
YEAH, WELL, MAYBE.
HUH.
SO WHY DON'T YOU HANG AROUND
WITH US UNTIL WE FIGURE OUT
WHAT THE PROBLEM IS?
[AKATSUKI AND SHIROE] HMM?
TELL HER ABOUT IT,
MR. STRATEGY.
[SHIROE] YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE SHOULDN'T
LEAVE HER ALONE.
AKATSUKI, DIDN'T YOU SAY YOU HAD
A THING AGAINST JOINING A GUILD?
[AKATSUKI] I CHOSE TO BE
AN ASSASSIN TO AVOID
ALL THE POLITICKING.
[SHIROE] YEAH, THAT'S
KIND OF WHY THE TWO OF
US AREN'T IN ONE EITHER.
BUT NOW THAT WE'RE NOT
IN FRONT OF A COMPUTER,
WE'RE PROBABLY BETTER
OFF BANDING TOGETHER
FOR OUR OWN SAFETY.
[AKATSUKI] YOU'RE SURE?
YOU REALLY WANT ME IN
YOUR PARTY, SIR SHIROE?
IT'D BE AWESOME TO HAVE
YOU ALONG, AKATSUKI.
OK.
[AKATSUKI] THEN FROM
THIS MOMENT ON, I SHALL
REVERE YOU AS MY LORD,
AS YOUR NINJA.
[SHIROE] MY NINJA? MY LORD?
[NAOTSUGU] ISN'T THAT
A SAMURAI'S JOB?
[AKATSUKI] YOU HAVE SAVED
ME FROM THE DIRE AND MOST
DISGUSTING FATE
OF BEING TRAPPED
IN A MAN'S BODY.
MY CODE OF HONOR
REQUIRES ME TO PAY BACK
THE DEBT I'VE INCURRED.
EVEN IF IT IS BUT
A SMALL KINDNESS,
IT SHALL BE REPAID.
I WILL BE YOUR NINJA AND
SERVE AS YOUR BODYGUARD.
(SPARKLES)
[SHIROE] UM, WELL,
THANKS FOR THAT, I GUESS.
[NAOTSUGU] HMM.
ALL RIGHT, TEAM,
LET'S DO IT.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] THE
NON‐PLAYER CHARACTERS THAT
INHABIT THE WORLD OF ELDER TALES
REFER TO THEMSELVES AS
"THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND."
(VENDOR SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
AND PLAYERS LIKE US,
WE ARE CALLED "ADVENTURERS."
[VENDOR] YOU GUYS WANT SOMETHING
TO EAT? YOU LOOK HUNGRY.
[NAOTSUGU] IS ALL THIS
STUFF REALLY FOOD?
(STOMACHS GROWLING)
[NAOTSUGU] I'LL STARVE IF I
WASTE TIME THINKING ABOUT IT.
RICE DUMPLINGS AND
GREEN TEA, PLEASE.
[VENDOR]
RIGHT. COME AGAIN.
[NAOTSUGU] THIS TASTES
LIKE DOG CRAP.
[SHIROE] IT'S BAD.
REALLY, REALLY BAD.
[AKATSUKI]
THIS IS SO WRONG.
[NAOTSUGU] IT FEELS
LIKE A SOGGY CRACKER,
AND THEY DIDN'T PUT
ANY FREAKING FLAVOR IN IT.
AND ALL THE DRINKS TASTE
LIKE UNFLAVORED WATER.
(CHIME)
HUH?
[NAOTSUGU] WHAT'S UP, HUH?
[SHIROE] SOMEONE'S CALLING ME.
[RINGING]
I WONDER WHO.
(GASPS)
[NAOTSUGU] IT WAS MARIELLE?
[SHIROE] YEAH.
SHE'S THE GUILD MASTER FOR
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE.
[NAOTSUGU]
THE GRAND GUILD HALL?
OUGHT TO BE CALLED
"BIG DOORY TOWN PLACE."
[SHIROE] EACH GUILD HALL
IS ITS OWN ZONE, NAOTSUGU.
[NAOTSUGU] ONLY THE REALLY WEIRD
STUFF STILL FEELS LIKE THE GAME.
[AKATSUKI] THAT'S A
WHOLE LOT OF... CUTE.
[NAOTSUGU] THIS IS THE
GUILD MASTER'S ROOM?
HA HA HA!
SHIROE!
[SHIROE]
MARIELLE. OOH!
(THUD)
[MARIELLE] ARE YOU OK?
YOU MUST BE HUNGRY!
EAT SOMETHING, EAT SOMETHING,
NOT THAT IT HAS ANY FLAVOR!
[SHIROE] CALM DOWN,
WILL YOU, MARIELLE?!
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
WHO'S THIS?
HMM.
[MARIELLE] SHIROE, DID YOU
GET A GIRLFRIEND AND NOT
TELL ME ABOUT HER?
[SHIROE] OF COURSE NOT! JEEZ!
[MARIELLE] WOW, YOU'RE
SO CUTE! YOU WANT A
LOLLIPOP OR SOMETHING?
SHIROE, ALL THESE
DAMN HOTTIES?
WHERE DO YOU
HIDE THEM ALL?
I HAVEN'T BEEN
HIDING HER.
[MARIELLE] OH, AND
WHO'S THIS BIG GUY?
[NAOTSUGU]
I'M NAOTSUGU.
WHAT'S UP? OH!
[MARIELLE] HO HO HO!
GOOD TO MEET YOU, NAOTSUGU!
WH‐WH‐WHA‐?
YOU'RE SO BUFFED UP,
AND YUMMY MUSCLES!
DO YOU LIFT WEIGHTS?
OH, I JUST LOVE
THE BEEFY PECS!
[NAOTSUGU] IT'S JUST
A SUIT OF ARMOR.
UH, DUDE, SHE'S...
SHE'S FREAKING ME OUT!
[WOMAN] MARIELLE, STOP IT!
[NAOTSUGU] WHOA!
ANOTHER ONE?
FREAKING HOTTIE PARADE!
BEST GAME EVER!
[SHIROE] HENRIETTA!
MY GOODNESS.
SIR SHIROE, I'M SORRY I ASKED
YOU HERE ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
[HENRIETTA] NOW, CONSIDERING
THE SITUATION WE'RE IN,
I'D LIKE TO
ASK YOU A FEW‐
(GASPS)
AH! SHE'S SO CUTE!
(FAWNING)
[SHORYU] AND THERE THEY GO,
WASTING THEIR TIME.
[AKATSUKI] YOU DON'T TOUCH ME!
[SHIROE] EXCUSE ME?
UH, MISS HENRIETTA?
DID YOU WANT TO
ASK ME SOMETHING?
[NAOTSUGU] SAVE ME!
[AKATSUKI]
SERIOUSLY, GO AWAY!
[SHIROE] TELL ME, HOW MANY
OF YOUR PEOPLE ARE HERE?
[MARIELLE] INCLUDING MYSELF,
19 OF US ARE ONLINE,
18 OF US ARE IN AKIHABARA,
AND THAT'S ALL THAT LOGGED IN.
AND IT'S SAFE
TO SAY WE CAN'T
CALL ANYONE ELSE.
ON TOP OF THAT, SHIBUYA,
MINAMI, SUSUKINO... ALL OF THEM.
ALL OF THE MAJOR JAPANESE
CITIES ON THE SERVER ARE
IN BAD SHAPE RIGHT NOW.
AND IF THAT WASN'T BAD ENOUGH,
NONE OF THE INNER CITY
TRANSPORT GATES ARE WORKING,
AND THAT MEANS
OUR USUAL METHOD OF
GETTING AROUND IS SHOT.
EVERYONE'S MEETING
WITH THEIR GUILDS NOW.
THEY'RE ALL LOOKING FOR
ANSWERS WITHOUT KNOWING
ALL THE QUESTIONS TO ASK.
AND IT LOOKS LIKE GUILDS
ARE STEPPING UP MEMBERSHIP
DRIVES FOR SELF‐PROTECTION.
[MARIELLE] LISTEN,
AT A TIME LIKE THIS,
THE MORE PEOPLE ON
YOUR SIDE THE BETTER.
[NAOTSUGU]
SO LIVING HERE IS NEW,
BUT EVERYONE STUCK HERE
IS AT LEAST FAMILIAR
WITH THE GAME, RIGHT?
THAT ISN'T
NECESSARILY TRUE.
[ALL] HUH?
[SHIROE] REMEMBER, THEY JUST
LAUNCHED THE EXPANSION PACK,
THE NOVASPHERE PIONEERS.
[AKATSUKI] OHH.
[NAOTSUGU] I GET IT.
IF THEY'VE ADDED THAT NEW
EXPANSION, THE ENTIRE
WORLD OF THE GAME...
FROM WEAPONS,
MONSTERS, AND QUESTS,
COULD BE WAY DIFFERENT
THAN IT USED TO BE.
(GOBLIN HOWLS)
[SHIROE] WHICH MEANS WE CAN'T
COUNT ON THIS WORLD BEING
ELDER TALES THE WAY WE KNEW IT.
[MARIELLE] WELL, LET
ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
[SHIROE] HMM?
HMM.
LOOK, SHIROE, I KNOW WE'VE
HAD THIS TALK, AND I KNOW
YOU'RE NOT A BIG FAN
OF ALL THE BACKBITING THAT
GOES ON IN THE GUILDS...
HMM.
[MARIELLE]
BUT... BUT THAT
WAS THEN, OK?
WOULD YOU THINK ABOUT
JOINING CRESCENT MOON?
UH, MARIELLE...
[MARIELLE] DEBAUCHERY TEA PARTY
ISN'T AROUND ANYMORE, RIGHT?
AND NOW WOULD
BE PERFECT TO‐
[SHIROE] I'M SORRY, MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE] OHH.
I JUST CAN'T
DO IT, NOT YET.
[NAOTSUGU] SHE'S A PRETTY
COOL GUILD MASTER.
SHE'S GOT ALL THAT
SEXY RESPONSIBILITY.
AND SHE WAS
NICE TO US.
[SHORYU]
THE DEBAUCHERY
TEA PARTY.
I HEARD THE TEA PARTY
WAS THIS AMAZING GUILD
THAT JUST PLAIN
WENT AND BROKE UP.
[MARIELLE] NOT REALLY.
THEY HAD A NAME AND ALL
BUT DIDN'T REGISTER.
[SHORYU] UH...
THE TEA PARTY USED
THEIR DIVERSITY TO CONDUCT
LARGE‐SCALE RAIDS AS A GROUP.
THEIR INDEPENDENCE
ALLOWED THEM TO COME
TOGETHER AT TIMES
OF THEIR OWN CHOOSING AND
WIN SOME LUCRATIVE BATTLES
WITH SHIROE AS THEIR STRATEGIST.
[PLAYER] HOW LONG ARE
WE GONNA BE STUCK HERE?
[NAOTSUGU] ARE THEY REALLY JUST
GONNA SIT THERE DOING NOTHING?
[SHIROE] HMM.
[NAOTSUGU] DO YOU SUPPOSE
DYING WOULD LET THEM OUT?
IT'S A PRETTY COMMON SCENARIO
IN ALL THAT FANTASY NOVEL CRAP.
[SHIROE] AND ANOTHER ONE IS
JUST STAYING DEAD AFTER YOU DIE.
[NAOTSUGU]
UH‐HUH. YEAH...
[AKATSUKI] DYING IN
THE GAME USED TO MEAN
RESURRECTION IN THE CATHEDRAL.
[NAOTSUGU] NICE, BUT I'M
NOT TESTING THAT OUT.
HMM.
[NAOTSUGU]
AND DUDE, I'M LEVEL 90.
I DON'T WANT TO
LOSE THAT, YOU KNOW?
[AKATSUKI] IS SOMETHING
WRONG, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] MAYBE WE
SHOULD TRY IT.
[NAOTSUGU] THE ARCHIVE
TOWER WOODS.
[SHIROE] WE'RE LEVEL 90...
THAT'S THE LEVEL CAP.
NORMALLY, LOW‐LEVEL MONSTERS
WOULD JUST IGNORE US.
BUT IN THIS AREA, ANYTHING
WILL JUMP US WHEN THEY SEE US.
SO WE SHOULD STAY ALERT.
[AKATSUKI] SOUNDS LIKE
THE PERFECT PLACE TO
EXPERIMENT, MY LORD.
[NAOTSUGU] DUDE, YOU
KNOW THE MINIMAPS DON'T
WORK OUT HERE, RIGHT?
HUH?
[AKATSUKI] BRIER WEASELS!
[SHIROE] THEY ARE LEVEL 28.
[NAOTSUGU]
AH, A LITTLE
WARMUP. COOL!
HUH? WHAT?
(WEASELS SHRIEK)
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU!
[NAOTSUGU]
I CAN'T WATCH THEM
AND ENTER MY ATTACK
COMMANDS! COME ON!
[SHIROE, THINKING] IT'S A BIG
JUMP FROM USING THE SYSTEM
AND MASTERING IT, I GUESS.
[SHIROE] STICK TO THE
FORMATION, GUYS.
[BRIER WEASELS SHRIEK]
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] I WAS
EXPECTING IT TO BE MORE PAINFUL,
BUT NAOTSUGU'S RIGHT.
IT'S NOT LIKE SITTING AT
HOME PLAYING WITH SOFTWARE.
WE ACTUALLY HAVE TO USE OUR
BODIES AND WHAT'S IN OUR HANDS
TO GET OUT OF THIS.
AND IT'S NOT GOING WELL.
OH, CRAP! I GUESS IT
WON'T BE A WARMUP AT ALL!
[SHIROE] AAH!
[NAOTSUGU] AH!
(TRIFFID ROARS)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] IF WE
WANT TO LIVE PAST THE NEXT
COUPLE OF DAYS HERE,
WE'D BETTER LEARN HOW
TO FIGHT IN THIS WORLD
ON ITS TERMS AND FAST.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
TO SHOW US HOW.
[SHIROE]
AKATSUKI!
HOW DID YOU
DO THAT?!
I‐I DON'T KNOW.
[COINS CLINK]
MY BODY JUST
MOVED ON ITS OWN.
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU,
DON'T USE YOUR MENU, OK?
JUST TRY FIGHTING
WITH YOUR BODY.
DUDE, I'LL DIE!
(WEASELS SHRIEKING)
[SHIROE] JUST DO IT!
[NAOTSUGU] I LOSE MY
LEVEL 90, IT'S YOUR ASS!
SHIELD SWING!
HUH?
THIS IS AMAZING!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
ELDER TALES...
OVER 20 MILLION PLAYERS
WORLDWIDE LOG IN TO
THIS MMO DAILY,
BUT HERE'S THE THING...
30,000 JAPANESE ADVENTURERS
AND AT LEAST SEVERAL
HUNDRED THOUSAND
AROUND THE WORLD ARE NOW
STUCK HERE IN THIS PLACE
THAT'S JUST LIKE
THE GAME ITSELF.
AND WE DON'T KNOW
HOW TO LEAVE.
NIGHTMARE SPHERE!
[NAOTSUGU]
CROSS SLASH!
ASSASSINATION!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
AND ALL OF US WHO WOUND UP
BEING A PART OF THIS EVENT
WOULD FOREVER REFER
TO THIS DAY AS...
THE APOCALYPSE.
(GIRL SOBS)
SERARA? WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
TALK TO ME!
[SERARA]
MISS MARIELLE, HELP ME...
[MAN 1]
THERE SHE IS.
[MAN 2] WE GOT
YOU NOW, SWEETHEART.
(WHIMPERING)
(MEN LAUGH)
[MAN 2] GET HER!
[MARIELLE] SERARA!
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
ONE DAY, WE FOUND OURSELVES
TRAPPED IN A MYSTERIOUS WORLD.
WE FOUGHT AND HURT ONE ANOTHER,
BUT IT WAS ONLY A GAME.
WE WEREN'T EVEN
ALLOWED TO DIE.
THEN, WHEN A YOUNG GIRL IN
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
RUNS INTO DANGER IN A
DISTANT NORTHERN LAND,
SHIROE SETS OUT ON A JOURNEY.
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.