[SHIROE] ALL OF THESE
ALTERCATIONS HAVE HAPPENED
IN THE SPAN OF ONLY 2 DAYS.
IT'S TOO MANY TO JUST
BE A COINCIDENCE.
[HENRIETTA] BUT WHY?
WHY WOULD SOMEONE WANT
TO ATTACK AKIHABARA?
[SHIROE] HM.
WHAT THEY'RE DOING IS SPREADING
THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE CITY
TO CAUSE MINOR DISTURBANCES
AND START GROUNDLESS RUMORS.
I'D SAY THEIR GOAL
SEEMS PRETTY SIMPLE...
TO DESTROY THE REPUTATION
OF THE ROUND TABLE.
[KARASHIN] THEN I
GUESS I WAS RIGHT.
[MINORI] YEAH, AND SHIROE
THINKS THE SAME THING, TOO.
AN ATTACK...
THE TRANSIENT 15% OF
THE CURRENT POPULATION
HAS CAUSED OVER
60% OF THE PROBLEMS.
SO YOU'RE SAYING THEY ACTUALLY
DELIBERATELY TURNED IN
FAULTY PAPERWORK
JUST TO CONFUSE US?
[MINORI] THE GUILDS
THAT ARE SUPPOSED TO
BE PROVIDING SECURITY
ARE SO BUSY DEALING WITH
THIS SUDDEN OUTBREAK OF
BICKERING AND PETTY PROBLEMS,
THEY CAN'T DO
THEIR REAL JOBS.
WELL, GOOD GRIEF!
WHO DO YOU THINK'S
BEHIND THIS?
(ELISSA SIGHS)
[ELISSA] I KNOW THIS MAY NOT
BE A NICE THING TO SAY,
BUT IF THIS WERE
MERELY A BANQUET TO
THANK THE ADVENTURERS,
I SERIOUSLY DOUBT YOU'D HAVE
TO GO TO ALL THIS TROUBLE.
YOU GET FURTHER WITH POLITENESS
THAN WITH PAGEANTRY.
[RAYNESHIA] YES, BUT WHY IS LORD
MARVESS CHOOSING TO SHOW UP NOW?
DO YOU THINK IT MIGHT
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH THE REVOLUTION THAT'S
BEEN BREWING UP IN THE WEST?
I DON'T KNOW.
[ELISSA] EITHER WAY,
HE REALLY ISN'T SOMEONE
WE CAN SIMPLY TURN AWAY,
NOW, IS HE?
[RAYNESHIA]
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
I KNOW.
IT'S JUST THAT‐
[ELISSA] WHAT IS IT?
I'VE GOT A BAD
FEELING ABOUT THIS.
WELL, SO LONG AS WE
REMEMBER THAT THE GOAL
OF TONIGHT'S BANQUET
IS TO DEEPEN OUR FRIENDSHIP
WITH THE ADVENTURERS.
YES, YOU'RE RIGHT.
AND I WILL DO MY BEST TO
BE BOTH CORDIAL AND POLITE
TO LORD MARVESS.
BUT THAT'S IT. DON'T EXPECT
MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
[ISAAC] AND THAT'S IT.
SOUNDS LIKE A BIG DEAL, HUH?
[SHIROE] THANKS FOR
THE LATEST INFO.
ALL RIGHT KEEP UP
THE GOOD WORK.
I TAKE IT THAT
WAS ISAAC.
YEAH, IT WAS.
[SHIROE] HE SAID A HIGH RANKING
WESTELANDIAN MERCHANT NOBLEMAN
NAMED LORD MARVESS HAS JUST
NOW ARRIVED IN THE CITY.
IS THAT A PROBLEM,
MY LORD?
WELL, LET ME SEE IF
I CAN EXPLAIN IT.
[SHIROE] I BELIEVE THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND ARE TRYING TO
ATTACK OUR CREDIBILITY.
[AKATSUKI]
"PEOPLE OF THE LAND"?
[HENRIETTA] WHY WOULD
THEY DO THAT?
[SHIROE] IN THE ORIGINAL
"ELDER TALES,"
THERE WERE NEVER ANY QUESTS
THAT INVOLVED AN ATTEMPT
TO REMOVE SOMEONE
FROM POWER.
AND IT ISN'T SOMETHING
ADVENTURERS WOULD EVER
NEED TO CONSIDER, RIGHT?
BESIDES, IT DOESN'T EVEN
SOUND LIKE IT WOULD BE
A VERY FUN QUEST ANYWAY.
NO, IT DOESN'T.
AND SO YOU BELIEVE THIS
WESTELAND NOBLEMAN
IS ULTIMATELY THE ONE
WHO'S TRYING TO DESTROY
THE ROUND TABLE'S
REPUTATION?
[SHIROE] WELL, GIVEN THE VAST
NUMBER OF PEOPLE OF THE LAND
INVOLVED IN THE DISTURBANCES,
THE ODDS ARE RELATIVELY
HIGH THAT SOMEONE IMPORTANT
IS RUNNING THINGS.
AT LEAST, THAT'S
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
[SHIROE] AND I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING THAT WOULD LEAD
ME TO THINK OTHERWISE.
[HENRIETTA] THEN OUR ADVERSARY
IS COMING FROM THE WEST.
[SHIROE] DON'T TELL ANYONE
ABOUT THIS FOR A WHILE.
[HENRIETTA] BUT I STILL DON'T
UNDERSTAND WHY ON EARTH HE
WOULD WANT UNDERMINE
THE ROUND TABLE.
[SHIROE] IT'S ONLY
ONE STEP IN A PLAN.
THE END GAME MUST
BE GREATER.
HE PROBABLY WANTS TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THE CONFUSION
IN ORDER TO INTERFERE WITH
THE TREATY BETWEEN EASTAL
AND THE ROUND TABLE.
HE DOESN'T WANT EASTAL TO
MONOPOLIZE ALL THE BENEFITS.
[HENRIETTA] WE NEED
TO ACT QUICKLY, THEN.
SHOULD WE CANCEL THE FESTIVAL
BEFORE IT GETS OUT OF HAND?
[SHIROE] I DON'T THINK
WE NEED TO DO THAT.
[HENRIETTA] AH...
[SHIROE] IF WE SUDDENLY
CANCEL THE FESTIVAL,
THEN IT CALLS INTO QUESTION OUR
ABILITY TO SOLVE PROBLEMS.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT HE WANTS.
INSTEAD, OUR BEST MOVE'S
PROBABLY TO JUST MINIMIZE
THE DAMAGE AND
WAIT THINGS OUT.
[HENRIETTA] AND HOW DO
WE DO THAT, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] WELL, WE MUST ASSUME
THAT THEY HAVE AT LEAST
ANTICIPATED THE POSSIBILITY
OF A COUNTERATTACK.
LET'S GIVE THEM ONE,
SHALL WE?
[SHIROE] AHH! EASY, AKATSUKI.
PUT THOSE AWAY.
[AKATSUKI] BUT, MY LORD,
IT'S TIME TO FIGHT, RIGHT?
[SHIROE] NO, NO!
I DIDN'T MEAN WE'D GO OUT AND
START CHOPPING PEOPLE UP, OK?
THIS TIME, WE WON'T
BE NEEDING THOSE.
(AKATSUKI GROANS)
[NAOTSUGU] REPORT TO YOU?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT] YES.
JUST KEEP ME CONSTANTLY INFORMED
ABOUT WHAT SORT OF PROBLEMS
POP UP AND WHERE THEY ARE, OK?
[NAOTSUGU] YOU GOT IT, BOSS MAN.
BUT, WAIT. I THOUGHT
ISAAC AND HIS BUDDIES
WERE ON DISTURBANCE DUTY.
[SHIROE] WE HAVE MORE
GROUND TO COVER THAN
I ORIGINALLY EXPECTED.
IT'S GOTTEN
MORE COMPLICATED.
SO IN ORDER TO SET UP
NEW CHAINS OF COMMAND
AND BRING IN MORE
PERSONNEL EFFICIENTLY,
I'M GONNA NEED
MORE INFORMATION.
[NAOTSUGU] CAN WE ASK THE
OTHER GUILDS TO HELP US OUT?
[SHIROE] IF THEY KNEW THE
ROUND TABLE WAS CONCERNED
ENOUGH TO TAKE ACTION,
IT WOULD GIVE THE ENEMY
EXACTLY WHAT THEY WANT.
SO WE NEED TO FIGURE
OUT WHO'S AVAILABLE
AND GET THEM TO HELP
WITHOUT THEM KNOWING
THAT THEY'RE HELPING.
SOUND ABOUT RIGHT,
STRATEGY MAN?
[SHIROE]
YEAH, SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
[AKATSUKI] AND THAT'S
THE SITUATION.
PLEASE KEEP
US INFORMED.
[TOYA] ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I'M ON MY WAY OUT.
[MINORI] OK.
[KARASHIN] SORRY YOUR
BROTHER GOT DRAGGED INTO
HELPING US OUT WITH THIS.
[MINORI] WELL, SHIROE'S
THE ONE WHO GAVE HIM THE ORDERS.
[TOYA] CLAIM CHECKS... CHECKS...
HE DID? TO MAKE
THINGS EASIER FOR US?
NOT EXACTLY.
I DON'T KNOW, REALLY.
[SHIROE] YEAH, IT MIGHT BE
BETTER IF YOU MET UP WITH TOYA.
THAT'S ABOUT IT, I THINK.
[MINORI] HUH? SO, UM, IS THAT
ALL YOU NEED FROM ME?
SHIROE, IF IT'S REALLY TRUE
THAT WE'RE UNDER ATTACK,
THEN ISN'T THERE
ANYTHING ELSE I CAN DO?
[SHIROE] THAT'S ALL.
THANKS, MINORI.
[MINORI, THINKING] I THINK
SHIROE WAS TELLING ME TO DO
WHATEVER I THINK IS
BEST FOR THE SITUATION.
HE'S ENCOURAGING ME TO
MAKE MY OWN DECISIONS ABOUT
HOW TO HELP OUR MISSION.
[TARO] HEY, GUYS, I JUST GOT
ANOTHER BATCH IN FROM THE SOUTH!
[MINORI] IF YOU'RE WORKING ON
THE REFUND FOR THE POTATOES,
I'VE GOT A FEW MORE.
[KARASHIN] I'M ON IT.
[MINORI, THINKING]
I MAY BE WRONG ABOUT THIS,
BUT IF THAT'S TRUE...
IF IT'S REALLY TRUE...
IF SHIROE WAS
COUNTING ON ME,
EVEN IF ONLY A
LITTLE BIT...
THEN I'M...
THEN I'LL‐
(THUD)
OH.
[TARO] MINORI, I'M SORRY,
BUT I ALSO HAVE THESE.
[MINORI] WHOA. SO WAIT. ARE
THESE ALL CLAIM CHECKS FOR
LUGGAGE?
[TARO] YEAH, WE JUST KEEP
GETTING MORE AND MORE WORK.
THE REAL DEAL'S
ABOUT TO START.
[MINORI] ALL RIGHT.
THEN I SHALL OUR DEFEND OUR
REAR LINE TO THE DEATH.
[KARASHIN AND TARO] HUH?
[MINORI, THINKING]
SHIROE HAS TAUGHT ME THE
FUNDAMENTALS OF HOW TO FIGHT.
FORMATION, OPERATOR,
FIELD MONITOR, PATROL FILE.
WHAT'S THE FIRST THING
THE FRONT LINE SHOULD DO?
AND WHAT ABOUT THE HEALER?
AND WHAT ABOUT THE REAR LINE?
[MAN 1] I DON'T HAVE ALL DAY...
[TOYA] OVER HERE! HEY, GUYS.
HEY, I'M WITH THE COUNCIL!
I'VE COME TO PICK UP
THE CLAIM CHECKS!
BACK HERE! I'M WITH
THE COUNCIL! HEY!
[MAN 2] WE'RE CUSTOMERS,
YOU KNOW!
[TOYA] THIS IS SO BAD!
[TOYA] IT REALLY IS A WAR!
[MAN 2] JEEZ, HOW LONG
DO WE HAVE TO WAIT?
[MINORI] THE PEOPLE WORKING
AT THE WAREHOUSE DESK
FIELDING THE ONSLAUGHT
OF COMPLAINTS...
THEY ARE OUR FRONT LINE.
[KARASHIN] RIGHT.
THE BASEMENT OF
WAREHOUSE 3.
[KARASHIN] ARE YOU
KIDDING ME?
[TARO] UH...
[KARASHIN] OK, THANKS.
I'LL SEND YOU THE VOUCHERS
AS SOON AS I CAN...
[TARO] I AM FREAKING OUT, MAN.
[MINORI, THINKING]
KARASHIN AND HIS FRIENDS
ARE DEALING WITH THE
OVERFLOW OF PROBLEMS
THE OTHERS
CAN'T HANDLE.
THEY ARE OUR HEALERS.
AND AS THEIR REAR LINE, IT'S
MY DUTY TO SUPPORT THEM ALL
AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE.
(BOXES FALLING)
[TARO AND KARASHIN] WOAH!
[CAT MAN] SORRY...
[TARO] YOU FREAKING IDIOT!
THOSE TOOK FOREVER TO ORGANIZE!
[CAT PERSON] WHAT'S WITH YOU?!
[TARO] WHAT'S WITH YOU?!
[KARASHIN] HEY, HEY,
HEY. EASY.
[MINORI] IT'S ALL
RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
[ALL THREE] HUH?
[MINORI] ACCIDENTS HAPPEN,
BUT WE'VE GOT TO KEEP OUR HEADS.
GETTING ANGRY
STOPS THE FLOW.
AND STOPPING THE
FLOW HURTS US.
[KARASHIN] "THE FLOW"?
UH, YEAH, SHIROE TOLD ME
WE NEED IT IN EVERY FIGHT.
[MINORI] AND THE FLOW OF
BATTLE ISN'T SOMETHING
YOU LEARN OR READ.
IT'S SOMETHING YOU BECOME.
[KARASHIN] OK, I FEEL
A BIT BETTER.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE SHIROE
HIMSELF IS HERE WITH US.
OH, NOT REALLY.
[KARASHIN] ALL RIGHT,
YOU GUYS. BECOME THE FLOW!
[BOTH] WHOO‐HOO!
[MINORI, THINKING] I'VE LEARNED
SO MANY TACTICS, TECHNIQUES,
AND GAINED SO MUCH
KNOWLEDGE FROM SHIROE.
BUT SOMEDAY, SOMEDAY
SOON, I HOPE...
I WANT TO BE ABLE TO GIVE
SOMETHING BACK TO HIM.
[AKATSUKI] WHAT?
"THIS POT IS A GOOD
POT"? I DON'T EVEN
KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
[HENRIETTA] YES, THE WEST
SIDE OF THE CATHEDRAL.
[SHIROE, THINKING] WHAT IS THIS?
THEY'RE REPEATEDLY
ATTACKING AREAS
THAT HAVE NO
STRATEGIC VALUE...
NO REAL WORTH AT ALL.
[SHIROE] WHAT'S GOING ON?
[HENRIETTA] UM, SHIROE, LOOKS
LIKE ANOTHER CARRIAGE HAS THROWN
A WHEEL, AND IT'S
BLOCKING THE ROAD.
[SHIROE] OK, I GOT IT.
THE WEST SIDE OF THE CATHEDRAL?
HM. THAT DOESN'T
MAKE SENSE EITHER.
[HENRIETTA] HUH?
EVEN IF THEY CLOSE OFF
THIS PATHWAY,
THERE ARE STILL PLENTY
OF WAYS AROUND.
AND THERE ARE OTHER
WAYS TO STOP TRAFFIC.
DOESN'T SEEM TO BE
ANY REAL POINT TO IT.
[SHIROE, THINKING] THERE MUST
BE SOMETHING MORE TO THIS.
THERE'S OBVIOUSLY
SOMETHING, BUT WHAT?
[CONSTANTAN] YEAH!
THE ROUND TABLE IS
MAKING OUT LIKE THIEVES!
THEY'RE ILLEGALLY TAKING
MOST OF THE PROFITS
RIGHT OUT FROM
UNDER OUR NOSES.
OH? WHAT WAS IT YOU WERE
SAYING ABOUT OUR ROUND TABLE?
[CONSTANTAN STUTTERS]
[ISAAC] HA! THAT'S
WHAT I THOUGHT.
YEAH, IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY'RE DEFINITELY TRYING
TO SMEAR OUR REPUTATION.
WHAT'S THE PLAN, VILLAIN?
[NYANTA] YEAH. THINGS ARE QUITE
CONFUSED OUT HERE AS WELL.
CLEARLY WE DON'T HAVE THE
RIGHT NUMBER OF PERSONNEL
TO HANDLE ALL THE ISSUES.
[SHIROE] REALLY? I EXPECTED
THINGS TO BE A MESS THERE,
SO I THOUGHT I SENT
A PRETTY FAIR NUMBER.
[NYANTA] THE PROBLEM IS, IS THAT
IT'S TAKEN TOO LONG TO RESOLVE
EACH INDIVIDUAL INCIDENT.
IN SOME CASES, SEVERAL
PEOPLE ARE BEING TIED UP
BEHIND A SINGLE MERCHANT
FOR AN ENTIRE HOUR,
SOMETIMES EVEN MORE.
MOST PEOPLE ARE JUST WAITING
IN LINES, GETTING IRRITATED.
AND SOME OF THE PROBLEMS ARE
SO PERSONAL OR CONTRIVED
THAT WE DON'T REALLY HAVE
A SOLUTION FOR THEM.
[MAN] I APOLOGIZED, DIDN'T I?
[WOMAN] YOU CALL
THAT AN APOLOGY?
[SHIROE] OH, YOU MEAN
DOMESTIC QUARRELS.
[NYANTA] WITH ALL OF THESE
COUPLES AROUND, I GUESS I
EXPECTED SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
BUT THERE ARE SO MANY.
AND TO BE HONEST,
RELATIONSHIPS, WELL,
GAMERS AREN'T VERY GOOD
AT DEALING WITH THAT
SORT OF STUFF, YOU DIG?
[SHIROE] TRUE, I GUESS. BUT
WHAT DO YOU THINK, CHIEF?
DO YOU THINK THAT IT'S
ALSO PART OF THE ATTACK?
[NYANTA] ARE YOU ASKING ME?
THAT'S RARE, BABY.
DOES THE VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES
HAVE SOME UNCERTAINTY?
UH, YEAH.
[NYANTA] LOOK, ANYTHING
YOU DON'T KNOW,
I PROBABLY AIN'T GONNA
KNOW EITHER, UNLESS
WE'RE IN THE KITCHEN.
BUT IN THE END, I CAN'T SAY
THAT I SEE ANY UNIFIED PURPOSE
TO ANY OF THEIR ACTIONS.
[SHIROE, THINKING] WHY? THE MORE
I THINK ABOUT IT,
THE LESS CLEARLY I CAN VISUALIZE
THE ENEMY'S OBJECTIVES. FIND IT.
THERE HAS TO BE SOME METHOD TO
THIS MADNESS. FIND IT, SHIROE!
THERE MUST BE SOME INTENT BEHIND
THIS SEEMINGLY RANDOM PATTERN!
SHUTTING DOWN TRAFFIC,
SPREADING RUMORS,
AND STARTING
MEANINGLESS DISPUTES,
DELIBERATELY SUBMITTING BAD
PAPERWORK, MINOR TAX FRAUD,
TRYING TO BRIBE US,
TYING UP STAFF WITH
COMPLAINTS ABOUT EVERYTHING.
IS IT A MULTILAYERED ATTACK
OR ARE THEY JUST MAKING IT
ALL UP AS THEY GO ALONG?
NO. BUT WHAT ARE THEY THINKING?
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE, THE MARINE
AGENCY JUST RECEIVED
A HUGE NUMBER OF PIZZAS
THEY DIDN'T ORDER!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD,
THE COCKROACHES SPOTTED
AT EAT‐TIL‐YOU‐DROP ALLEY
WERE MADE OF RUBBER!
THEY'RE FAKE!
PIZZA? COCKROACHES?
[SHIROE] THIS IS DUMB.
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE?
[SHIROE, THINKING] THIS IS
ABSOLUTELY RIDICULOUS.
THEY DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING IN MIND AT ALL.
THEY'RE NOT THINKING ABOUT
ANYTHING. IT'S IRRATIONAL!
EACH OF THEIR ATTACKS IS
COMPLETELY IMPROVISED.
EVERYTHING'S INVENTED
ON THE SPOT!
SO NO MATTER HOW MUCH WE
STRESS OVER FIXING IT,
IT'S UTTERLY POINTLESS.
I HATE ENEMIES LIKE THESE.
I HATE MEANINGLESS, RANDOM,
SMORGASBORD, CLUTTERED INSANITY!
(SCREAMS)
[SHIROE, THINKING]
GET IT TOGETHER, SHIROE.
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
IF YOU'RE LIKE THIS.
BUT IF YOU DON'T REACT
AND DO SOMETHING PRETTY SOON,
PEOPLE WILL NOTICE
THAT SOMETHING'S UP.
HOW CAN I FIGHT AN ENEMY THAT'S
THIS SPORADIC AND UNPREDICTABLE?
WELL, NOW IF IT ISN'T
MASTER SHIROE.
[GUILD MEMBERS]
LONG TIME, NO SEE!
HEY, GUYS.
[SOUJIRO] OH, THE FOLKS
AT THE CAKE BUFFET
WERE REALLY NICE TO US!
[GUILD MEMBER] YEAH!
[DOLCE] OH, TOTALLY.
[SHIROE] THEY WERE NICE TO YOU?
[SOUJIRO] YEAH! THEY GAVE
ME A TON OF WHOLE CAKES.
(KANAKO GROWLS)
[SOUJIRO] AND IT WAS
WAY TOO MUCH FOR ME,
SO I CALLED IN ALL THE
OTHER GUILD MEMBERS.
[KANAKO] AH!
[GIRLS] "SOUJIRO!"
[KANAKO] CHARGE!
[SOUJIRO] AND EVERY TIME
A NEW MEMBER ARRIVED,
THEY WERE KIND ENOUGH
TO BRING US ANOTHER CAKE.
[SHIROE] I'M NOT SO SURE IF
I'D CALL THAT KINDNESS.
(KANAKO GROANS)
[NAZUNA] WE ATE THEM ALL!
[KAWARA]
GIVE US SOME MORE!
[ISAMI]
I WANT STRAWBERRY
TART, TOO.
[DOLCE] YOU WANT SOME
MORE, SWEET CHEEKS?
BY THE TIME WE HAD 30 OR SO,
SHE SAID SHE WAS OUT.
[SHIROE] HUH?!
[SOUJIRO] WHAT?
[SHIROE, THINKING] HE KEPT
BRINGING MORE PEOPLE,
AND THEY KEPT
BRINGING MORE CAKES
UNTIL THEY RAN
OUT OF CAKE?
HE FOUGHT THEM OFF BY BRINGING
IN A BUNCH OF... GIRLS?
[SOUJIRO] THE ORANGE MOUSSE
WAS REALLY SOMETHING SPECIAL.
LIKE A LINGERING
SCENT OF SUMMER.
[GROUP] YEAH!
[SHIROE, THINKING] IN REALITY,
THAT MIGHT HAVE BEEN
THE PERFECT COUNTERATTACK TO
THE CAKE GIRL'S SINISTER PLANS.
AND SINCE HE HAD NO IDEA
WHAT HE WAS DOING,
HE WAS KIND OF
INVINCIBLE IN A WAY.
[SHIROE] WAIT! HEY, YOU GUYS
CAME AT THE PERFECT TIME! HA HA!
[SOUJIRO] ARE YOU OK, SHIROE?
(GIRLS FAWNING)
[SHIROE] I THINK I HAVE
THE PERFECT JOB FOR YOU.
I'M GONNA NEED YOUR HELP.
HUH?
(GUILD MEMBERS LAUGHING)
[SHIROE, THINKING] I'VE GOT
THE ANSWER. I'VE GOT THE
ANSWER RIGHT HERE.
I'VE GOT A BUNCH OF
OBLIVIOUSNESS THAT CAN
BEAT THEIR RANDOMNESS.
[GUILD MEMBERS]
YOU ARE SCARING US.
[DOLCE] OH, MY GOODNESS. YOU ARE
SO SCARY, I CAN'T EVEN STAND IT!
(LAUGHTER)
[RAYNESHIA] AND, FURTHERMORE,
THANKS TO ALL OF YOU,
BOTH MAIHAMA AND
EASTAL WERE SAVED.
I CANNOT EXPRESS
MY GRATITUDE ENOUGH.
[ADVENTURER 1] NO, NO.
NO. DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
AS ADVENTURERS, IT'S OUR
JOB TO DO STUFF LIKE THAT.
[ADVENTURER 2]
WE GOT PAID AFTER ALL.
[ADVENTURER 3] IT WAS
NOTHING, REALLY. HEH HEH.
THEY'RE ALL BLUSHING
LIKE LITTLE CHILDREN.
BUT IT IS RATHER REFRESHING
INSTEAD OF BEING FLATTERED
OR FAWNED OVER
FOR NO REASON OTHER
THAN MY STATUS.
(ASSISTANT WHISPERING)
[RAYNESHIA] OH?
[ELISSA] PRINCESS, WE'VE JUST
RECEIVED WORD THAT LORD MARVESS
WILL BE MAKING HIS
APPEARANCE VERY SOON.
[RAYNESHIA] OK.
[ELISSA] HE'S ARRIVED
WITH A SHIP CARRYING
AN EXTREMELY LARGE
AMOUNT OF CARGO.
AND, UNFORTUNATELY...
[RAYNESHIA] IS THERE A PROBLEM?
[ELISSA] THIS HAS ALL
DEVELOPED SO SUDDENLY.
AND THERE'S MUCH MORE
THAN WE ANTICIPATED.
AND IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
DEALT WITH IN ADVANCE.
(CROWD GASPING)
[RAYNESHIA] AH?
[CAT ADVENTURER]
WHO'S THE FREAKY GUY?
[ADVENTURER WITH GOATEE]
MAYBE HE'S A NOBLEMAN.
[ADVENTURER WITH SPIKY HAIR]
HE HAS ADVENTURERS GUARDING HIM.
WHERE IS HE FROM?
[CAT ADVENTURER] IS THIS
LIKE A QUEST OR SOMETHING?
'CAUSE HE SEEMS SORT
OF A BIG SHOT.
[MARVESS] OH, WELL, NOW,
HOW DELIGHTFULLY LOVELY!
IF I REMEMBER CORRECTLY,
YOU MUST BE THE MUCH
LAUDED COWEN GIRL, YES?
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA, IS IT NOT?
[RAYNESHIA] THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING TO THE BANQUET
AS WE CELEBRATE
OUR FALL FESTIVAL.
[MARVESS CHORTLING]
[MARVESS] I'M ABSOLUTELY TICKLED
TO SEE IT SO SUCCESSFUL!
BUT IT WOULD SEEM
TO BE ENCUMBERED
BY QUITE A LACK OF ORDER.
[RAYNESHIA] AH...
[MARVESS] I NOTICE A RABBLE
OF COMMONERS ATTENDING THE
SAME BANQUET AS NOBLES.
THAT FORM OF BOLDNESS MUST BE
UNIQUE TO YOU EASTERN PEOPLE
REGARDLESS OF BEARING
THE MERCHANT GOD'S BLOOD
IN YOUR VEINS, HMM?
[ADVENTURER IN FUR HAT]
EASY THERE, OLD TIMER.
LET'S HAVE A TOAST, OK?
(PUNCH)
(CRASH)
ADVENTURERE IN FUR HAT:
HEY, DUDE, WHAT WAS THAT FOR?!
[MARVESS] PRESUMPTUOUS FILTH!
[RAYNESHIA] UH!
[ELISSA] PRINCESS.
I'M VERY SORRY, SIR.
PLEASE COME THIS WAY.
[ADVENTURER IN FUR HAT]
NO, NO, I'M FINE.
IT DIDN'T HURT OR ANYTHING.
I'M SORRY IF I SCREWED
UP YOUR PARTY.
[RAYNESHIA] UH, I DO APOLOGIZE
FOR HIS UNFORTUNATE
BREACH OF ETIQUETTE.
PERHAPS WE CAN MAKE IT UP TO
YOU WITH SOME EASTERN SAKE,
IF IT IS TO YOUR
LIKING, OF COURSE.
[MARVESS SNIFFS]
[MARVESS] HMM...
(CROWD MUTTERING)
HM. AH.
[EIJIRO] ARE YOU LOOKING
FOR A FIGHT HERE?
YOU DO KNOW WHAT
THAT WOULD MEAN, RIGHT?
WOULDN'T END WELL.
[MARVESS] NOW, THEN, PRINCESS,
I WOULD LIKE FOR YOU TO PREPARE
A WAREHOUSE FOR MY GOODS
AND CHATTELS AT ONCE.
WE CANNOT ALLOW OUR SEAFOOD
TO LOSE ITS FRESHNESS
BEFORE THE FESTIVAL,
NOW, CAN WE?
[RAYNESHIA] ABSOLUTELY. I WILL
SPEAK TO SOMEONE IMMEDIATELY.
PLEASE GIVE ME‐
[MARVESS] WHAT?! SPEAK
TO SOMEONE! WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'VE SENT ALL THE
APPROPRIATE PAPERWORK.
I SENT AN IDENTICAL MESSAGE
TO LORD SERJIAD AT MAIHAMA,
AND I RECEIVED APPROPRIATE
CORRESPONDENCE IN RETURN.
UNBELIEVABLE.
I WAS ASSURED YOU WOULD BE
PREPARED TO RECEIVE ME.
I HAVE BROUGHT THE FINEST
QUALITY MERCHANDISE
NORMALLY RESERVED FOR
THE LIKES OF ROYALTY,
SUCH AS YOURSELF, PRINCESS.
THEY MUSTN'T BE TREATED WITH
THOUGHTLESS OR CARELESS HASTE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
[KAWARA] OK. RIGHT
OVER HERE, EVERYBODY!
[ISAMI] HEY THERE, SWEETIE PIE!
NO CUTTING IN LINE, PLEASE, OK?
[MEN] HUH?
[NAZUNA] IT'S FINE.
WE CAN TAKE ALL YOUR
PAPERWORK HERE, HANDSOME.
[SHIROE, THINKING] THIS IS
WORKING BETTER THAN I EXPECTED.
[DOLCE] EXCUSE ME.
EXCUSE ME, STRATEGIST?
UH, STRATEGIST SHIROE...
[SHIROE] OH, YEAH,
DOLCE, WHAT YOU NEED?
[DOLCE] I'VE GOT 5
MORE LOVELIES FOR YOU.
THEY'RE ALL SPIFFIED UP AND
READY FOR THE FRONT LINES!
[SHIROE] UH, WHERE'S SOUJIRO?
[BLONDE WOMAN] SOUJIRO IS
CURRENTLY IN THE TOWN SQUARE
ON A HOT, ROMANTIC DATE
WITH 10 DIFFERENT GIRLS, SIR.
I MEAN, ON PATROL.
[BRUNETTE] SIR, RIGHT NOW,
PLATOON 4 IS CURRENTLY
WITH HIM, SIR!
[SHIROE] OK, THEN LET'S
MAKE CONTACT WITH HIM.
PLATOON 4 IS GOING TO
SWITCH OUT WITH PLATOON 5.
AND THEN THEY WILL CONTINUE
TO PATROL THE AREA.
[DOLCE] ROGER, DODGER.
ALL OF US IN PLATOON 5
ARE MOUNTING UP
FOR A PATROL WITH MR. SOUJI‐POO.
[NYANTA] OH, YEAH, NOW I GET IT.
A GROUP DATE UNDER THE AUSPICES
OF PATROLLING. STRAIGHT PIMPIN'.
[SHIROE] COULD YOU PLEASE
NOT PUT IT THAT WAY?
BUT, YEAH, MORE THAN 20 PLATOONS
OF SOUJIRO'S FANGIRLS ARE
ON PATROL ALL OVER AKIHABARA.
IT'S GREAT. THESE GIRLS ARE TIED
BY THE BONDS OF SISTERHOOD.
AND THEY INHERENTLY USE
THEIR CHAIN OF COMMAND
TO ORGANICALLY FORM
TACTICAL GROUPS.
EACH DEALING WITH
TROUBLE IN A FLEXIBLE AND
BEAUTIFULLY HONEST MANNER.
THEY'RE STOPPING PROBLEMS
BEFORE THEY EVEN START.
ON STRATEGIST SHIROE'S
ORDERS, WE'RE HERE TO
SWAP DUTIES WITH YOU!
[PLATOON 4] AW!
[DOLCE] SORRY, LADIES.
[NAZUNA] AND THEIR
MOTIVATION IS PRETTY SIMPLE.
BECAUSE IF
THEY PARTICIPATE,
THEN THEY GET A CHANCE
TO BE CLOSER TO SOUJIRO.
[ISAAC] IS THAT
SERIOUSLY ALL IT IS?
[NYANTA] MM‐HMM.
THAT'S RIGHT, BABY.
THE PLAN IS A
HUGE SUCCESS.
[SHIROE] YEAH.
TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
I WASN'T SURE A PLAN
LIKE THIS HAD ANY CHANCE
OF WORKING SO WELL.
AND ALL WE CAN DO TO FIGHT
THIS EVIL, DASTARDLY ATTACK
IS SEND OUT AS MANY
AWESOME HOT CHICKS AS WE
POSSIBLY CAN. I LOVE IT!
THEIR CHAIN OF COMMAND
IS INDEED SOLID.
THEY'RE DEALING WITH
PROBLEMS IN AN ORGANIZED
AND EFFICIENT MANNER.
[NAZUNA] UH‐HUH!
[GIRL] OH!
[NYANTA] THAT'S RIGHT.
IT AIN'T EASY TO CAUSE TROUBLE
WHEN YOU'RE SURROUNDED BY
BEAUTIFUL YOUNG
HONEYS. FOR REAL.
[GIRL] AWW!
[NYANTA] AND SINCE THE LADIES
ARE EXPERTS AT ROMANCE,
THEY'RE A NATURAL
FIT TO HANDLE
ALL THOSE PESKY
RELATIONSHIP ISSUES.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, I'M
PRETTY SURE I WOULD HAVE
SCREWED THAT UP BIG‐TIME!
THANKS TO SOUJIRO FOR
MAKING THIS THING POSSIBLE.
[NAZUNA] HE REALLY
IS DREAMY, ISN'T HE?
[SHIROE] HA HA.
[AKATSUKI] YOU SEEM TO BE
ACTING RATHER ODDLY, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] WELL...
[AKATSUKI] ARE YOU
JEALOUS OR SOMETHING?
[SHIROE] UH!
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?!
[NYANTA] I'M NOT SO SURE IF HE'S
JEALOUS. MAYBE MORE ANNOYED.
OR PERHAPS THE WORD
IS "INADEQUATE"?
(SHIROE SIGHS)
[ISAAC] WHATEVER YOU CALL IT,
WISH I HAD AN ARMY LIKE THAT.
(LAUGHTER)
[AKATSUKI] HMM?
[ISAMI] EXCUSE ME,
STRATEGIST.
I HAVE A MESSAGE FROM
THE SECURITY TEAM AT
WATERMAPLE MANSION.
[SHIROE] THANKS.
[KAWARA] THAT'S WHERE
THE PRINCESS IS HOLDING
THE BANQUET, RIGHT?
[AKATSUKI] DID SOMETHING
ELSE HAPPEN?
[SHIROE] I HAD OUR
GUYS LOOK INTO IT.
THE BIG SHOT FROM THE WEST
JUST SHOWING UP IN AKIHABARA.
HE MAY BE BEHIND ALL THIS.
[ISAAC] HE'LL BE AFTER THE
PARTY HE'S NEGOTIATING WITH.
THAT MAKES THE MOST SENSE.
MAYBE AFTER THE
VERY SAME PRINCESS
WHO HAPPENED TO MOVE
HERE FROM MAIHAMA, HMM?
[SHIROE] ALL RIGHT, CHIEF.
I'M LEAVING YOU IN CHARGE
HERE FOR A WHILE.
[NYANTA] ROGER THAT.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE
SITUATION HERE, MY LORD?
I HAVE A LITTLE PLAN
FOR THAT, AKATSUKI.
[SHIROE] IF THEIR GOAL IS TO
TEAR THE AKIHABARA PEOPLE APART,
TO CREATE A RIFT
AMONGST EVERYONE HERE,
WE JUST NEED TO MAKE THE
SCALE FESTIVAL MORE FUN,
AND ENSURE THAT ALL THE GUESTS
HAVE AS MUCH FUN AS POSSIBLE.
SO IF WE'RE GONNA
DO IT RIGHT,
LET'S SET OFF A
BUNCH OF FIREWORKS.
UH?
[ELISSA] WELL, THE DOCUMENTS
ARE LEGITIMATE, PRINCESS.
I'M NOT EXACTLY SURE HOW,
BUT ALL I CAN GUESS IS
THAT WE SOMEHOW MESSED
UP AND MISSED THEM.
WE COULDN'T HAVE.
[MARVESS] SO AM I TO ASSUME
THAT YOU WERE NOT PREPARED,
THOUGH I GAVE YOU AMPLE
WARNING OF MY NEEDS?
WELL, GOODNESS
GRACIOUS ME ALIVE!
IS THIS TRULY THE MANNER IN
WHICH THE COWEN FAMILY OPERATES?
HONESTLY, IT'S MAKING
ME QUESTION YOUR
FLAWLESS REPUTATION.
I MEAN, HOW EVER DID YOU
ESTABLISH SUCH FAVORABLE
RELATIONS WITH AKIHABARA?
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
I JUST NEED TO APOLOGIZE
AND SETTLE THIS
MATTER PEACEFULLY.
OHH, IF ONLY I COULD
POSTPONE THIS ORDEAL
UNTIL AFTER THE BANQUET.
[SHIROE] GOOD EVENING.
[RAYNESHIA] AH?
[MARVESS] HM?
[ADVENTURER 1] HE'S WITH
THE ROUND TABLE.
[ADVENTURER 2] YEAH?
[SHIROE] HI THERE.
HOW'S IT GOING?
UH, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] I'VE COME TO GET YOU,
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
[RAYNESHIA] AH?
[MARVESS] AND JUST WHO
ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO BE?
A FRIEND OF HERS.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
IT SEEMED THE END WAS NEAR.
BUT, IN FACT, IT WAS
ONLY THE BEGINNING.
THE TRUE THREAT APPEARS
BEFORE SHIROE.
THE COAL BLACK QUEEN.
A WHITE FLOWER BLOOMING
IN THE DARKNESS.
THEIR ENCOUNTER WILL
CHANGE HISTORY AND OPEN
THE CURTAIN ON A NEW STORY.
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] WE WILL
CHANGE THE WORLD.