(GROWLING)
[KAWARA] TIGER ECHO FIST! HYAH!
[SOUJIRO] HYAH! UGH!
I CAN'T AGGRO THAT
MANY STINKING FISH.
HEY, WEST WIND, YOUR
AOE SPELL... HOW MUCH
TIME DO YOU NEED?
[KAWARA] MY NAME'S KAWARA,
YOU IDIOT. AND IT'S ABOUT
20 SECONDS.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
[SHIGERU]
I WISH I COULD SAY FASTER.
[SOUJIRO, THINKING] FOR A
PICKUP GROUP, OUR TEAMWORK
REALLY ISN'T THAT BAD.
BUT THERE ARE JUST SO MANY.
(SAHUAGIN GROWLS)
[SHIGERU] WE NEED TO HOLD OUT
UNTIL THE NEW KIDS CAN REACH
THE SAFE ZONE INSIDE THE FOREST!
[KAWARA] THAT'S RIGHT.
I'M NOT GOING BACK TO
MY MASTER A FAILURE!
HM.
THERE'S WAY TOO MANY.
THIS IS THEIR SIXTH PATROL.
WHAT THE HELL'S
UP WITH THAT?
IT'S STRANGE.
THE ENCOUNTER RATE FOR
GOBLINS IN THIS AREA
SHOULD NOT BE THIS HIGH.
HMM.
EVERYONE'S IN QUITE
A HURRY, MY LORD.
HMM.
[SERJIAD] WHAT? DID YOU
SAY "GOBLINS"?
[NYANTA] AN ARMY OF
A FEW THOUSAND GOBLINS IS
ON THE MOVE JUST BEYOND
THE NEXT RIDGE, HMM.
[REZARICK] THAT MANY?
[NAOTSUGU] ANY NEWS FROM THE
PEOPLE WE LEFT ON THE BEACH?
[NYANTA] I CAN'T REACH MARIELLE
OR SHORYU ON THEIR TELEPATHICS.
THEY'RE NOT ON MY FRIEND LIST.
(BEEPING)
[NAOTSUGU] NOW THAT
YOU SAY IT, CHIEF,
I DON'T THINK I ADDED
ANYONE FROM CRESCENT MOON
TO MY LIST EITHER.
HMM, WE BLEW THAT
ONE FOR SURE.
I CAN'T REACH THE OTHER
MEMBERS OF THE BLACK
SWORD KNIGHTS EITHER.
MAN, THIS IS A
DOOKIE SANDWICH.
OK, NOW, TELL ME, WHAT
DID THE ARMY LOOK LIKE?
THE ONES I SAW MARCHING DOWN
THE CENTER OF THE VALLEY
WERE A MAJOR RAIDING FORCE, HMM.
I'VE NEVER SEEN AN ARMY
THAT SIZE IN ALL THE
TIME I'VE BEEN A PLAYER.
THERE WERE ALSO HOBGOBLINS
AND TROLLS AND DEMON BEASTS.
I REALLY COULDN'T TELL
YOU ANYTHING MORE THAN
THEY SEEMED TO BE
HEADED WEST‐BY‐SOUTHWEST
WHEN I SAW THEM.
[MINORI] SO THE GROUPS
WE FOUGHT MUST HAVE BEEN
SCOUTING PATROLS, RIGHT?
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE.
[TOYA] AND WHERE'S
THEIR ARMY NOW?
[RUDY] OVER THAT MOUNTAIN?
[MINORI] WE SHOULD HAVE
EVERY ONE OF THE MEMBERS OF
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
ON OUR FRIENDS LIST.
I MEAN, DON'T WE?
[ISUZU] YEAH.
[MINORI] OK. CAN YOU
CALL THEM AND ASK
WHAT'S HAPPENING OVER THERE?
(BEEPING)
RIGHT. I'LL GO AHEAD AND LET
SHIROE KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
[SHIROE] ALL RIGHT.
KEEP ME IN THE LOOP ON THIS.
[NAOTSUGU] WILL DO.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
UM, MY LORD?
[NYANTA] A MASS OF BLUE
GOBLINS FROM THE COAST?
[NAOTSUGU] SAHUAGIN?
WE USUALLY DON'T SEE THOSE
UNTIL WE'RE FURTHER SOUTH.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
I'M NOT SURE.
MAYBE A COINCIDENCE.
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
THEY JUST TOLD ME THAT
EVERYONE WHO IS ON THE COAST IS
NOW TRYING TO MAKE THEIR WAY
BACK TO THE SCHOOL BUILDING.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE NEED A PLAN
OF ACTION, NAOTSUGU‐CHI.
WELL, IF PUSH COMES TO
SHOVE, WE COULD ALWAYS USE
A RETURN SPELL TO GET
BACK TO AKIHABARA.
IF WE DO DECIDE TO DO THAT,
JUST REMEMBER IT'LL TAKE
US SEVERAL DAYS TO COME
BACK HERE TO ZANTLEAF.
[NYANTA] THEN WE SAVE THAT
AS OUR LAST RESORT.
[NAOTSUGU] MARIELLE'S IN
CHARGE OF THE TRAINING
CAMP BACK AT THE BEACH.
WE'LL TRY MEETING UP WITH HER.
(CHIME)
[ISAMI] THEY'RE CALLING.
[SOUJIRO] OK, DO IT.
[ISAMI] ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE.
THANK YOU FOR STANDING BY FOR
THIS EMERGENCY TELEPATHY CALL,
CONNECTING YOU WITH SHIROE,
THE LEADER OF THE
LOG HORIZON GUILD.
[SHIROE] I'VE TAKEN THIS
UNUSUAL ACTION OF CONVENING
A TELEPATHIC CONFERENCE
BECAUSE THE MEMBERS OF
THE ROUND TABLE
CANNOT MEET IN PERSON.
AND THE SITUATION FACING
US IS VERY URGENT.
I KNOW THIS MAY NOT BE IDEAL,
BUT I NEED ONE PERSON
AT EACH LOCATION
TO CREATE A RELAY.
THIS IS THE ONLY WAY WE CAN ALL
COMMUNICATE WITH EACH OTHER.
I DO PLAN ON DEVELOPING THIS
NETWORK FURTHER IN THE FUTURE.
[SHIROE] ANYWAY, LET'S GET
EVERYBODY UP TO SPEED.
THIS MORNING ON THE
ZANTLEAF PENINSULA,
WE CONFIRMED ATTACKS BY
MULTIPLE RACES OF DEMI‐HUMANS.
[SHORYU] DOWN AT
THE COAST, THERE ARE
SEVERAL HUNDRED SAHUAGIN.
AND THAT'S A
CONSERVATIVE ESTIMATE.
[SHIROE] AND WE ALSO OBSERVED
A LARGE RAIDING FORCE OF GOBLINS
IN THE FOREST.
THEIR TOTAL NUMBERS
STAND AT 10,000.
[ISAAC] 10,000?! REALLY?!
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
I BELIEVE THERE MIGHT EVEN BE
MORE OF THEM WAITING IN RESERVE.
MASTER SHIROE, DO YOU HAVE ANY
IDEA WHY THIS IS HAPPENING?
AND WHAT MIGHT BE THEIR
MOTIVATION FOR DOING THIS?
YES, BUT IT'S ONLY
A THEORY FOR NOW.
[SHIROE] DO YOU REMEMBER THE
"GOBLIN KING'S RETURN"?
"THE GOBLIN KING'S RETURN"?
[KRUSTY] IF I REMEMBER
CORRECTLY, THAT WAS A REGULAR
EVENT FOR BUILDING EXPERIENCE.
[SHIROE] RIGHT.
THE GOBLIN CASTLE, SEVENTH FALL,
LIES DEEP WITHIN THE FOREST
OF THE OUU TERRITORY.
TWICE A YEAR, THE GOBLIN KING
IS RECORONATED THERE.
BEFORE THAT HAPPENS, PLAYERS
ARE GIVEN A WEEK TO SLAY HIM.
IF THEY DEFEAT THE KING
BEFORE THE CORONATION,
THEY CAN ACQUIRE RARE ITEMS.
SINCE MOST OF THESE
ITEMS WERE VERY POWERFUL,
AND IT WAS AN EASY EVENT FOR
REGULAR PLAYERS TO ACHIEVE,
IT WAS ONE OF THE GAME'S
MOST POPULAR EVENTS.
THE GOBLIN KING IS
USUALLY THE MAIN CHIEF.
THE LEADER OF ONE OF THE OUU
AREA'S MOST POWERFUL CLANS.
IN OTHER WORDS, BY ATTACKING
GOBLIN BASES AND STRONGHOLDS
AROUND THE ENTIRE AREA,
YOU COULD WEAKEN THEM,
THUS WEAKENING THE POTENTIAL
GOBLIN KING HIMSELF.
IN THEORY, OF COURSE.
[SHIROE] THERE WAS
SOMETHING ELSE, THOUGH.
I IMAGINE EVERYONE ELSE
FORGOT ABOUT IT.
IN FACT, I DON'T THINK IT
EVER ACTUALLY HAPPENED.
YOU MEAN WHAT THE ADMIN
SAID WOULD HAPPEN IF THE
GOBLIN KING WAS EVER CROWNED.
IT'D BE CHAOS.
ALL OF THE GOBLIN CLANS WOULD
STOP FIGHTING AMONG THEMSELVES,
UNIFY, AND THEN START ENGAGING
EVERYONE AS ONE MASSIVE ARMY.
[SHIROE] HMM.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
[NYANTA] I REMEMBER THAT, HMM?
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SINCE WE SHOWED UP,
WE'VE PUT SO MUCH EFFORT
INTO MAKING THIS WORLD LIVABLE,
WE FORGOT ALL ABOUT IT.
[ISAAC] I KNOW ME AND MY GUYS
HAVE BEEN SPENDING MOST OF
OUR TIME LEVELING UP.
WE REALLY HAVEN'T BEEN
THINKING OF TAKING ANY QUESTS
FROM THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND.
SO THIS IS WHAT
HAPPENED, HUH?
OK, THEN DOES THAT MEAN
THE GOBLIN FORCES ARE CURRENTLY
AT THEIR FULL STRENGTH,
MASTER SHIROE?
WE HAVE TO ASSUME THAT
THAT'S THE SCENARIO THAT'S
CURRENTLY FACING US.
THE GOBLIN KING HAS A UNITED
ARMY FAR STRONGER THAN WE'VE
EVER SEEN IN THE PAST.
AND WHAT'S WORSE, WE REALLY
DON'T KNOW THE ORIGINAL SIZE
OF THE 6 MAJOR GOBLIN CLANS.
AND THAT'S NOT GOOD.
WE WERE OUTNUMBERED AT ZANTLEAF,
BUT IF WE RAISED AN
ARMY OF OUR OWN,
WE COULD EASILY
WIPE THEM ALL OUT.
[MICHITAKA] HMM.
THE PROBLEM WITH THAT
IS THE EASTAL LORDS.
NONE OF THEIR COMBINED
ARMIES HAVE THE STRENGTH TO
HANDLE THIS ONE ON THEIR OWN.
[ISAAC] YEAH, LIKE I
CARE ABOUT THEM.
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY ASKED
US FOR HELP ANYWAY.
[SOUJIRO] WHEN THIS
WAS STILL A GAME,
THERE WAS AN ARMY
WITH AMAZING POWER.
UH, WHO WERE THEY AGAIN?
[HENRIETTA] THE IZUMO KNIGHTS.
[MICHITAKA] YEAH.
THEY WERE HEROES BORN STRAIGHT
FROM THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
AND THE IZUMO KNIGHTS ARE
FAR STRONGER THAN ANY OF US.
THE ULTIMATE WEAPON OF
THE HUMAN RACE.
[MICHITAKA] SUPPOSEDLY, THERE
ARE 13 BANDS OF KNIGHTS ALL
OVER.
AND EVERY TIME THEY GET
INVOLVED IN A FIGHT,
IT'S FOR THE FATE OF THE WORLD.
THE IZUMO KNIGHTS ARE SUPPOSEDLY
THE DESIGNATED GUARDIANS
FOR THE YAMATO ARMIES.
THEN WE SHOULDN'T HAVE
TO WORRY ABOUT IT.
WE SHOULD SINCE WE
DON'T KNOW WHETHER THEY
REALLY EXIST OR NOT.
HUH?
SOMEONE GETS HIS
NEWS FAST.
AT THIS POINT, A LARGE BATTLE
WITH THE GOBLINS IS UNAVOIDABLE.
SOME PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO DIE OUT THERE.
WE HAVE THE LUXURY
OF COMING BACK TO LIFE.
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
AREN'T SO LUCKY.
PLEASE, MY LORD.
[ELISSA] PRINCESS?
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA?
LOOKS LIKE HE DIDN'T
SHOW UP TODAY, DID HE?
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[ELISSA] YOUR FRIEND, KRUSTY.
[RAYNESHIA] WHAT?
[ELISSA] THE TWO OF YOU
HAVE BEEN SEEING EACH
OTHER FOR BREAKFAST
LATELY, PRINCESS.
IT'S ONLY NATURAL FOR YOU
TO EXPECT HIM TO SHOW UP.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
[BOTH] HMM?
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
[RAYNESHIA] WHAT IS IT, FATHER?
[PHENEL] RAYNESHIA,
I NEED YOU TO LISTEN.
HUH?
THE GOBLIN ARMY IS APPROACHING
THE OUTSKIRTS OF THE CITY...
10,000 OF THEM.
FATHER!
[PHENEL] AND, OF COURSE,
THEY WILL BUILD UP THOSE
FORCES BEFORE ATTACKING.
OUR WORST FEARS
HAVE BEEN REALIZED.
[ELISSA] THERE ARE 30,000
PEOPLE IN MAIHAMA.
AND OUT OF THAT, BARELY 2,000
WORK IN SECURITY FORCES.
I AM RETURNING TO MAIHAMA
TO SHORE UP ITS DEFENSES.
WAIT! I'M COMING
WITH YOU!
YOU WILL REMAIN HERE IN THE
PALACE AND KEEP YOURSELF SAFE.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[PHENEL] YOUR GRANDFATHER
IS STAYING HERE, TOO.
BUT WHY WOULD HE?
[PHENEL] THE ISSUE IS
LARGER THAN MAIHAMA'S
SAFETY, RAYNESHIA.
ALL THE LORDS MUST REACH
A CONSENSUS OF ACTION
WITH THIS CONFERENCE.
AND AS THE HIGH LORD
OF EASTAL,
MY FATHER MUST REMAIN HERE
TO MAKE SURE THAT HAPPENS.
AND YOU WANT ME TO
STAY BEHIND AND HELP?
[PHENEL] IT'S FOR
THE BEST, RAYNESHIA.
(DOOR CLOSES)
DON'T LEAVE ME.
[MARIELLE] ALL RIGHT!
WE'RE ALL HERE!
I WAS THINKING WE'D HAVE
CURRY TONIGHT. YUMMY, RIGHT?
(SHORYU GROANS SOFTLY)
[NAOTSUGU] MARIELLE.
[SHORYU] HUH?
[MARIELLE] NAOTSUGU!
[SERARA] MARIELLE!
[MARIELLE] OH, GOOD!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE SAFE!
IT'S LIKE THE BEST NEWS EVER.
YOU'RE STILL REALLY A
LITTLE KID, AREN'T YOU?
[SERARA] YEAH, BUT‐
[MARIELLE] THANKS, NAOTSUGU.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS...
[NAOTSUGU] HM?
[MARIELLE] FOR NOT
ANTICIPATING THE ATTACK.
WAIT. WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S NOT LIKE IT WAS
YOUR FAULT, MARIELLE.
HMM, IF ANYTHING,
EVERY SINGLE ADVENTURER
OUT THERE IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS DISASTER, HMM?
YEAH, I GUESS.
NONE OF US THOUGHT
IT THROUGH, OK?
LET BRAINIAC SHIROE
FIGURE THIS THING OUT.
EVEN IF IT MEANS
GAMING THE SYSTEM,
HE'LL FIND A WAY FOR US
TO KICK THIS PUPPY.
(MARIELLE LAUGHS)
SHE'S SMILING...
YOU REALLY SHOULD CONSIDER
A CHANGE OF CLOTHES, MARIELLE.
IT'S STARTING TO GET
CHILLY‐CHILL OUTSIDE.
[MARIELLE] EH?
[NAOTSUGU] THAT'S RIGHT.
[MARIELLE] OH!
GIVE ME A SECOND.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[NYANTA] MEOW.
AND I'M BACK, OK? HUH?
[NAOTSUGU] PUT OUT THESE FIRES.
[MARIELLE] WHAT'S HAPPENING?
[NAOTSUGU] OVER THERE.
[NYANTA] EASILY A
THOUSAND TORCHES, HMM?
[MARIELLE] A GOBLIN ARMY?
[NAOTSUGU] THAT'S RIGHT.
I NEED A MAP, GUYS. HURRY!
[MARIELLE] HOW'S IT
LOOKING, GUYS?
[NYANTA] HMM, IT LOOKS LIKE
WE HAVE A PROBLEM, HMM?
YEAH?
WELL, MAYBE IT'S NOT
EXACTLY ACCURATE TO SAY
THAT THE GOBLIN PROBLEM IS OURS,
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
LOOK, JUST COME OUT
AND SAY IT, MR. RETIREE.
[NYANTA] IT LOOKS LIKE
THE GOBLINS ARE PREPARING
EN MASSE TO LAY SIEGE
TO THE TOWN OF CHOSHI.
AH...
THE GOOD NEWS IS THAT THIS
ISN'T THE GIANT ARMY I SAW.
IT'S A BIT MORE OF A
MEDIUM‐SIZED DIVISION, HMM?
THE MAIN ARMY IS
STILL WAY UP NORTH
JUST OUT OF OUR REACH.
WHAT DO THEY WANT
WITH THE TOWN?
THEY WANT TO STRIP
THEM TOTALLY BARE
BECAUSE AS BIG AS
THEIR FORCE IS,
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR FOOD FOR
THE REST OF THEIR ARMY.
(MARIELLE GASPS)
[MINORI] YEAH, BUT CHOSHI
DOESN'T HAVE ANY FORTIFICATIONS.
[MARIELLE] NO, THEY DON'T.
[MINORI] IF WE JUST
SIT BACK AND WATCH,
THEY WON'T EVEN LAST
UNTIL MORNING.
WE CAN'T RETURN TO AKIHABARA
WITHOUT ACCOMPLISHING ANYTHING.
[TOYA] WE NEED TO HELP THEM.
[NAOTSUGU] HM.
THAT'S RIGHT. I DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT WE CAN DO TO HELP,
BUT IT'S BETTER THAN JUST
STAYING HERE, ISN'T IT?
[ISUZU] DON'T BE CRAZY.
[MINORI] ISUZU?
THIS ISN'T THE DUNGEON.
I MEAN, WE DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW MANY OF THOSE THINGS
WE'RE UP AGAINST.
THAT'S ABSOLUTELY
TRUE, MISS ISUZU.
BUT ALL THOSE PEOPLE IN
CHOSHI DON'T EVEN KNOW
THE GOBLINS ARE COMING.
AND YOU WANT TO SIT
HERE AND DO NOTHING.
I WANT TO LET THE GROWNUPS
TAKE CARE OF THIS, OK? PLEASE?
ARE YOU SAYING WE'RE
JUST A BUNCH OF KIDS?!
[ISUZU] THAT'S NOT IT!
[RUDY] WE'VE BEEN
DOING SOME PRETTY GOOD
LEVELING UP, ISUZU.
[SERARA] OH, JUST
STOP IT, YOU GUYS.
[MINORI] I MUST SAY THAT I AGREE
WITH RUNDELLHAUS ON THIS ONE.
BUT I DON'T THINK
THAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT
WHETHER WE'VE
LEVELED UP OR NOT.
BUT, MINORI...
I'M ASKING YOU, PLEASE
LET US GO TO CHOSHI.
[ADULTS] HMM...
[SOUJIRO] NO MATTER HOW
BIG THEIR ARMY IS,
THEIR NUMBERS DON'T
POSE MUCH THREAT.
WITH OUR 1,500 MEN, WE SHOULD
BE ABLE TO DESTROY THEM.
[ISAMI] YEAH, BUT YOU
HEARD ISAAC DURING
OUR LAST CONFERENCE.
IF THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
HAVEN'T ASKED US FOR HELP,
HE THINKS WE SHOULDN'T
BOTHER OFFERING.
ISAAC NEEDS A GOOD REASON TO
FIGHT BEFORE JUST JUMPING IN.
[SOUJIRO] UH, YEAH, THAT'S
PROBABLY TRUE, I GUESS.
AND SHIROE DIDN'T REALLY SEEM
VERY MUCH LIKE HIMSELF, DID HE?
HUH?
NORMALLY HE'D JUST MAKE
A QUICK DECISION
AND JUST GO WITH
IT, YOU KNOW?
[SHIROE] I'VE ASKED
SOUJIRO'S WEST WIND
BRIGADE TO JOIN US HERE.
HE WON'T HESITATE TO HELP US
OUT IF WE GET ATTACKED.
[MICHITAKA] ALL OF
THE REPRESENTATIVES
OF THE NOBLES ARE HERE.
WE CANNOT LEAVE IT UNPROTECTED.
THEY'RE SMALL
BUT POWERFUL.
AND THAT'S GOOD.
THE LAST THING WE NEED TO
DO IS ALARM THE NOBILITY.
I'M ALL FOR IT.
HAVEN'T HEARD ANYTHING.
YOU'D THINK THEY WOULD
HAVE OFFERED IT TO US
AS A QUEST OR SOMETHING.
I'M SURE THAT ISN'T
STOPPING THEM
FROM TALKING ABOUT IT
AMONGST THEMSELVES.
[MICHITAKA] WITHOUT INCLUDING
US IN THE CONVERSATION?
NOT GOOD, PEOPLE.
[KRUSTY] SO THEN DO WE PROPOSE
SOMETHING TO THEM, STRATEGIST?
BEFORE WE DO, THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO SHARE WITH ALL OF YOU.
[MICHITAKA] WHAT IS IT?
[SHIROE] IT'S ABOUT
DEATH IN THIS WORLD...
HOW IT REALLY WORKS.
(AKATSUKI GASPS)
[SHIROE] DEATH ALWAYS BRINGS
US BACK TO THE CATHEDRAL HERE.
BUT THE PRICE OF RESURRECTION
HAS ALWAYS BEEN AN EXPERIENCE
POINT PENALTY.
THAT'S AN EASY PRICE
TO PAY IN A GAME.
BUT THE PROBLEM JUST HAPPENS
TO BE THAT IT DOESN'T WORK
THE SAME WAY NOW.
[KRUSTY] HMM.
[SHIROE] FROM THE
INFORMATION I'VE GAINED,
THE DEATHS OF OUR BODIES ON
THE BATTLEFIELD HAS A REAL
ELEMENT OF RISK TO IT NOW.
I'LL SPARE YOU THE GORY DETAILS.
BUT IT SEEMS THAT EACH DEATH
COSTS YOU SOME OF YOUR MEMORIES.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
OUR MEMORIES?
(KRUSTY GASPS)
[MICHITAKA] SO EXACTLY
HOW MUCH WILL GET LOST?
[SHIROE] I'M NOT SURE.
[MICHITAKA] WELL, WHICH
MEMORIES DO WE LOSE?!
[SHIROE] I'M NOT SURE.
WHAT ARE YOU
SAYING, THEN?!
I DON'T KNOW!
WELL, NOT YET ANYWAY.
[SHIROE] HOWEVER,
THE FACTS ARE UNDENIABLE.
WE NEED TO BE CAUTIOUS.
I GET IT. IT'S THE ONLY
EXPLANATION THAT I'VE HEARD
FOR ALL THESE MEMORIES I'VE
LOST SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE.
[KRUSTY] I'M CONVINCED.
[MICHITAKA] HUH?
D. D. D. IS A WARRIOR GUILD
FIGHTING ALL THE TIME.
BEFORE THE INITIATIVE TO
ESTABLISH THE ROUND TABLE
AND BRING PEACE TO AKIHABARA,
I ORDERED MY GUILD TO UNDERGO
RIGOROUS COMBAT TRAINING.
I DIED A FEW TIMES OUT THERE.
I REALLY DIDN'T
THINK MUCH OF IT.
BUT OVER TIME, I CAN'T HELP
BUT NOTICE THAT SOME MOMENTS OF
MY LIFE ARE MISSING.
THAT'S SO SAD.
THAT'S HORRIBLE, MAN.
CAN YOU TELL WHAT
MEMORIES ARE MISSING,
SHORT‐TERM OR LONG‐TERM?
WELL, THAT'S
HARD TO SAY.
I MEAN, THEY ARE MEMORIES
I LOST, AFTER ALL.
BUT THEY DO ALL HAVE
SOMETHING IN COMMON.
AH...
[KRUSTY] I'VE DIED TWICE
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE.
I'VE ONLY LOST A FEW MEMORIES,
BUT I'M ALMOST POSITIVE
THEY ARE ALL FROM
THE REAL WORLD.
IT'S LIKE MY FORMER LIFE IS
STARTING TO DRIFT AWAY.
NOW, I KNOW MY MEMORY
IS PRETTY SHARP,
BUT OCCASIONALLY I HAVE
THESE MOMENTS, LIKE
REMEMBERING I HAD A CAT
BUT NOT HIS NAME OR
WHAT HE LOOKED LIKE.
IT'S ODD TO
SAY THE LEAST.
THIS IS ONLY MY
EXPERIENCE WITH IT,
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH, I GUESS.
A DEATH OR TWO SEEMS TO BE
ONLY MILDLY INCONVENIENT.
SO I SUPPOSE EVEN A FEW
DOZEN MIGHT NOT CAUSE
YOU THAT MUCH TROUBLE.
COME ON, KRUSTY.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT GOING
COMPLETELY OUT OF TOUCH
WITH THE WORLD YOU CAME FROM.
WE FORGET THE REAL WORLD?
LET'S NOT RUN THE RISK
OF OVERREACTING TO THIS.
JUST TRY NOT TO GET
YOURSELF KILLED.
[KRUSTY] OF COURSE, IF WE START
FAILING TO ACT OUT OF FEAR OF
DYING OVER AND OVER AGAIN,
ISN'T THAT LIKE BEING ONLY
HALF‐ALIVE IN THE FIRST PLACE?
HMM...
[MARIELLE] IT'S WAY
TOO RISKY, YOU GUYS.
[TOYA] WHY? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?!
[RUDY] HOW CAN YOU BE
AN ADVENTURER IF YOU'RE AFRAID?!
[SERARA] CALM DOWN, EVERYBODY!
LISTEN TO ME, WE NEED TO
LET EVERYONE IN EASTAL
HANDLE THIS, OK?
RIGHT NOW I'M THE ONE
RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR SAFETY.
AND I SAY WE SHOULDN'T
ACT ON OUR OWN.
[NYANTA] THIS IS GOING
TO AFFECT RELATIONS
BETWEEN THE ADVENTURERS
AND THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
FOR A LONG, LONG TIME TO COME.
[REZARICK] AND WE HAVE
NO OSTENSIBLE REASON
TO SAVE THEM, DO WE?
YOU'VE GOT TO LOOK
AT THE BIG PICTURE
AND KEEP YOUR FEELINGS
IN CHECK ON THIS ONE.
NO MATTER HOW HARD
IT IS TO DO SO.
[RUDY] ALL RIGHT!
I'LL GO IF NOBODY ELSE WILL.
[ISUZU] COME ON, RUDY!
IT'S DANGEROUS.
[RUDY] YEAH, BUT‐‐
WE ARE A PARTY, AREN'T WE?
[ISUZU] IF WE JUST GO
OUT THERE AND WE'RE NOT
ALL IN THIS TOGETHER,
WE'RE GOING TO GET HURT,
JUST LIKE BACK IN THE DUNGEON.
BUT WE CAN'T DO NOTHING!
[MINORI] HM.
[TOYA] AH.
HERE'S A THOUGHT, HOW ABOUT
YOU LET US GO AS AN ADVANCE
SCOUTING PARTY?
[RUDY]
A SCOUTING PARTY?
THAT WAS A STROKE
OF GENIUS, MISS MINORI.
[SERARA] WE CAN AT LEAST
HELP THEM EVACUATE, CAN'T WE?
[MINORI] SERARA, I ONLY
SAID THAT SO THEY'D
AGREE TO LET US TAKE OFF.
[TOYA] SO THAT MEANS...
[MINORI] I THINK WE SHOULD DO
WHAT WE CAN TO PROTECT THE CITY.
[SERARA] HM.
(TOYA CHUCKLES)
BUT WHY?
NO ONE ASKED US.
AND THERE'S NO REWARD.
AND IT'S NONE OF OUR BUSINESS,
AND I WANT TO LIVE.
THERE ARE A LOT OF
REASONS NOT TO HELP.
I GET IT.
[MINORI] BUT I ONLY NEED ONE
GOOD REASON TO HELP.
YEAH, I SEE YOUR POINT.
CHECK IT OUT.
(FIRE SMOLDERING)
[SERARA] NO, NO, NO.
[RUDY] WE'RE SO CLOSE.
GOBLINS HAD TO
BE BEHIND THIS.
[TOYA] IS ANYONE THERE?!
(CREATURES HISSING)
[TOYA] UGH.
(GROWLING)
[TOYA] UH!
(TOYA GROWLS)
(TOYA YELLING)
TOYA!
I'VE GOT YOUR BACK,
ALL RIGHT, TOYA?
FLASH NEEDLE!
[TOYA] HEAD SPLITTER!
(COINS JINGLING)
[TOYA] YOU STILL NEED A REASON?
HOW ABOUT DOING THE RIGHT
THING 'CAUSE IT'S RIGHT?
IF YOU WANT TO HELP SOMEONE,
ISN'T THAT ENOUGH?
THAT'S WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE AN ADVENTURER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I BELIEVE IT NOW.
YOU CANNOT BE AN
ADVENTURER AND RUN AWAY.
[RUDY] WE CAN'T JUST
MARCH BACK HOME TO AKIHABARA
WITHOUT SAVING THIS TOWN.
[ISUZU] SO HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO PROTECT A TOWN
WITHOUT ANY WALLS FROM AN ENTIRE
ARMY OF GOBLINS, MR. TOUGH GUY?
FIGHTING SPIRIT, OF COURSE!
[ISUZU] WE'RE BACK TO YOUR
STUPID NONSENSE AGAIN?
[RUDY] UH!
[ISUZU] USE YOUR HEAD
FOR A CHANGE!
[RUDY] I AM!
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
THERE'S A WAY TO DO IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, ISUZU.
A PARTY OF FIVE DOESN'T STAND
A CHANCE DEFENDING A TOWN
AGAINST A DIVISION OF GOBLINS,
NOW MATTER HOW STRONG
WE'VE BECOME.
AND, BESIDES,
EVEN IF WE SUCCEED,
HOW MANY OTHER TOWNS FALL?
SO THAT'S WHY WE
WON'T PROTECT THEM.
[RUDY] WHAT?!
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?!
HM!
[NYANTA] MINORI‐CHI HAS
THE RIGHT IDEA, BABY.
[NAOTSUGU] WE CAME TO MAKE
SURE YOU LITTLE KNUCKLEHEADS
WEREN'T GETTING
YOURSELVES INTO TROUBLE.
AFTER ALL, US OLD FOLKS HAVE
TO LOOK OUT FOR YOUR SAFETY.
[SERARA] NYANTA!
[TOYA] MASTER NAOTSUGU!
UM, I'D LIKE TO ASK
PERMISSION...
GIRL, AN ADVENTURER DOESN'T
REQUIRE PERMISSION FROM ANYONE.
I CAN ALREADY TELL THAT
YOU'VE THOUGHT THIS THROUGH
FOR YOURSELF AND HAVE REACHED
YOUR OWN CONCLUSIONS.
YOU'RE NOT EXACTLY
CHOOSING SOMETHING EASY
THIS TIME, MINORI‐CHI.
[TOYA] WE KNOW WHAT WE'RE DOING.
WE'RE GOING OUT THERE
AND THERE'S NOTHING YOU
CAN DO TO STOP US!
MINORI'S GOT AN IDEA
HOW TO DEAL WITH THIS!
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH, YEAH. I GET IT.
BUT IF YOU'RE SO
CONFIDENT IN THAT IDEA,
WHY DON'T YOU DO US A FAVOR
AND TELL US ABOUT IT FIRST?
[MINORI] SURE. IT'S OBVIOUS
WE CAN'T PROTECT THE TOWN.
INSTEAD WE GO ON OFFENSE.
(CLANG)
AND WE ATTACK
THE GOBLINS INSTEAD.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
MINORI AND THE OTHERS
BEGIN THEIR BATTLE
AGAINST THE GOBLIN ARMY.
WE HAVE NO REASON BUT TO HELP
PROTECT THOSE AROUND THEM.
THAT IS THE FREEDOM
OF AN ADVENTURER.
BUT FREEDOM REQUIRES RESOLVE.
WHEN A GIRL BREAKS OUT OF HER
SHELL AND MAKES HER DECISION,
HER BODY WILL RISE INTO THE SKY,
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.