[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] THIS WORLD
HAS ONE TYPE OF CURRENCY: GOLD.
[SHIMMER]
[CORK POPS]
THE STANDARD COST FOR
THE ITEMS IN A SINGLE MEAL
IS AROUND 5 GOLD.
A NIGHT AT A CHEAP INN
IS 10 GOLD.
SO BASICALLY IT TAKES
ABOUT 35 GOLD PER DAY
TO TAKE CARE OF
LIFE'S NECESSITIES.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
JUST BEAT 6 GOBLINS
IN COMBAT.
AND ADVENTURERS CAN PUT
THEIR MONEY AND ITEMS
IN THE BANK LOCATED
IN THE GUILD BUILDING.
THIS PREVENTS OTHER
PLAYERS FROM STEALING IT.
NOW, OF COURSE,
EACH PLAYER ONLY GETS
LIMITED SPACE.
[SHIROE] I'M GONNA NEED
SOME MONEY TO MAKE IT WORK.
5 MILLION IN GOLD.
SHIROE, EVEN IF WE
CASHED IN ALL OUR GOODS,
CRESCENT MOON'S TREASURY
WOULD ONLY HAVE 60,000.
SERIOUSLY, SHIROE!
LIKE, WHAT'S ALL
THE MONEY FOR?
HM.
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
[GRUNTING]
[SHORYU] YOU KNOW
THESE ARE EASIER TO
KILL THAN CATCH, RIGHT?
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH, AND IF
YOU KILL THEM,
THEY JUST GO
AND TURN INTO
INGREDIENT ITEMS.
RIDICULOUS.
HOW IN THE HELL
DOES 200 KILOS OF
PORK OVER HERE
TURN INTO ONLY
2 KILOGRAMS OF FOOD?
[NAOTSUGU]
RIGHT? THAT'S WHY
WE'RE CATCHING THEM.
IF YOU GET A GOOD CHEF
IN YOUR KITCHEN,
HE CAN USE THE
WHOLE THING!
(GROWLING)
SUEY, BOYS!
LET'S DO THIS!
OUR QUOTA FOR
TODAY IS 60.
[HIEN] RIGHT.
COOL! IF IT'S
FOR MARIELLE,
I'LL GET ALL 60 MYSELF!
UM...
[LILIANA]
DOES THAT SEEM
A LITTLE BIT TIGHT?
[ASHLIN]
SOMETHING EASIER TO
MOVE IN WOULD BE NICER.
[ASUKA] COME ON, YOU GUYS,
LET'S SEE IF WE HAVE ANY
CLOTHES IN THE BANK.
[ASHLIN] OK!
CAN YOU TAKE A
TASTE OF THIS, CHIEF?
[NYAN‐TA] AH, LET'S
HAVE A LOOK HERE.
HMM. IT COULD USE
SOME SALT...
AND MAYBE JUST A HINT
OF CORIANDER AS YOUR
SECRET INGREDIENT.
[GHIROV]
RIGHT! THANK YOU!
OH! HE'S SO AWESOME!
(FLIES BUZZING)
(MARIELLE SIGHS)
I HAVEN'T LEFT THE
ROOM FOR 3 DAYS.
I CAN'T TAKE
THIS ANYMORE.
AND WE NEED TO HAVE
ALL OF THESE REGISTERS
APPROVED ALSO.
DOUBLE‐CHECK THE
FIGURES BEFORE WE
ASSUME THE MONEY'S THERE.
[MARIELLE]
WAIT! IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT'S TOTALLY IMPOSSIBLE!
[HENRIETTA] OH, I'M
SURE YOU'LL DO FINE.
YOU KNOW MATH AND
PAPERWORKY STUFF
ISN'T REALLY MY THING.
[MARIELLE] YOU'RE
THE GUILD MASTER,
SO YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO APPROVE THE BUDGET.
[MARIELLE] SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
SHUT YOUR FACE, UMEKO!
[HENRIETTA] UGH!
DON'T USE MY REAL NAME!
[MARIELLE] UMEKO! UMEKO! UMEKO!
[HENRIETTA] HNG!
(THUD)
[BOTH] HUH?
I'VE BROUGHT MORE, MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE]
SHIROE, YOU'RE, LIKE,
TOTALLY THE DEVIL.
I'VE GONE AHEAD AND COMPILED
A LIST OF EVERYTHING YOU
REQUESTED FROM US.
[SHIROE]
NOW, THAT WAS QUICK. HMM.
THE NUMBERS LOOK
ACCURATE, TOO.
OUR TREASURER IS
A FRICKIN' PIECE OF WORK.
IT'S LIKE SHE
ENJOYS TORTURING
HERSELF WITH BUNCHES
OF STUPID NUMBERY CRAP.
NO. I'M JUST GOOD
WITH TAKING CARE
OF THE BOOKKEEPING,
MARIELLE DARLING.
WHAT REALLY MAKES
THIS SPECTACULAR IS
HOW MERCILESS SHIROE'S PLAN
IS TURNING OUT TO BE.
HE OUGHT TO HAVE EVERYONE HE
MEETS START ADDRESSING HIM
AS "MR. SUPERVILLAIN."
THIS PLAN MIGHT QUALIFY
ME TO BE A SUPERVILLAIN,
BUT IT'S NOTHING LIKE
MARIELLE'S PAPERWORK SKILLS.
[HENRIETTA] I AGREE
WITH THAT. HA HA!
(SHIROE LAUGHING)
[MARIELLE] I GIVE UP.
(HENRIETTA SIGHS)
THE WORKLOAD REALLY
IS TAXING.
I'M AFRAID I'M
GOING TO NEED OUR DEAR
LITTLE AKATSUKI AROUND
TO KEEP ME GOING ALL
THROUGH THE DAY.
I'M AFRAID I'VE GOT
HER DOING SOMETHING
ELSE FOR ME RIGHT NOW,
BUT SHE MIGHT
HAVE A MINUTE.
[HENRIETTA] OH!
HA HA. OH!
(AKATSUKI SHUDDERS)
I'M STUCK INSIDE A GAME SERVER,
SO HOW CAN I BE CATCHING A COLD?
[MAN WITH SCARF] HERE'S THE
TAKE FOR THIS WEEK.
THIS WAS A GREAT WAY
TO EARN MONEY.
[MAN IN FEATHER CAP] HEH HEH!
THANKS FOR THE CASH, MAN.
TELL ISAAC HELLO FOR ME.
[MAN WITH SCARF] HEY, I HEARD
YOU STARTED DEALING IN
LEATHERWORKING, TOO.
[MAN WITH FEATHER CAP]
24/7, MAN. WE GOT PEOPLE WORKING
AROUND THE CLOCK AND FAST, TOO.
[NYAN‐TA] WELL, BLESS
ALL 9 OF MY LIVES.
THIS IS QUITE A HAUL, YO.
[NAOTSUGU] NOW IT'S
UP TO YOU, CHIEF.
[MARIELLE] (SQUEALING)
OH! NAOTSUGU, THANK
YOU! THANK YOU!
[NAOTSUGU] WHOA! OH,
COME ON. COME ON. COME ON.
I'M NOT A BODY PILLOW,
YOU DINGBAT!
MARIELLE, BEHAVE YOURSELF!
SHORYU AND HIEN,
THANK YOU BOTH, TOO.
[HIEN] HE SEEMED
REALLY MOTIVATED.
[SHORYU] UH, NO, I JUST
OUTWORK YOU, YOU SLACKER!
OH, WHATEVER,
LOVER BOY.
LOYAL LITTLE
PUPPY DOG!
DID A FOX JUST
CALL ME A DOG?!
BUT, LIKE, THERE STILL
TOTALLY ISN'T ENOUGH.
[BARKING]
[SHORYU] I'M ON IT!
[AIRPLANE FLYBY]
[MARIELLE] SHORYU'S
TOTALLY INTO THIS.
I DON'T EVEN
UNDERSTAND IT.
YOU GO GET THAT
MEAT, SHORYU!
[HIEN CHUCKLES]
[WOLF HOWLING]
[MARIELLE]
YOU ARE KILLING ME!
[HENRIETTA] THIS IS
ALL THE PAPERWORK.
NOW I CAN RETURN TO MY OWN JOB.
YOU'RE JUST AN
EVIL PERSON.
YOU AND SHIROE ARE DEMONS!
[BOTH] READY FOR BUSINESS!
[HENRIETTA]
OH, IT'S WONDERFUL!
[LILIANA]
CUTE AND DISTINCTIVE.
[ASUKA] OH, MY GOD. YOU GUYS,
THAT LOOKS ABSOLUTELY AMAZING!
[LILIANA]
WE'RE ALMOST DONE NOW.
[ASHLIN] AWW...
[HENRIETTA] IT'S FINALLY TIME.
[SHIROE] WHAT DO YOU
THINK, HENRIETTA?
[HENRIETTA] HMM?
[SHIROE] I KNOW THAT YOU
MENTIONED YOU'RE AN
ACCOUNTANT WITH AN MBA.
DO YOU THINK MY PLAN
HAS ANY MERIT AT ALL?
[SHIROE] I THINK IT'S
GOT A GOOD CHANCE.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO NOW IS
RAISE THE MONEY WE NEED
AS QUICKLY AS WE CAN.
[SHIROE] WE DON'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT WHERE IT CAME FROM
OR EVEN WHO WAS GIVING IT TO US.
RIGHT NOW WE'RE IN A TERRA NOVA
SITUATION WITH NO LAWS.
SO LET'S NOT RESTRICT
OURSELVES BY MAKING UP
A BUNCH OF NEW ONES.
[HENRIETTA] HMM.
[HENRIETTA, THINKING]
THIS WORLD HAS NO RULES.
IN OTHER WORDS,
WE CAN MAKE UP OUR OWN.
WE NEED A NEW RULE
TO MAKE MONEY,
A WAY TO MAKE PEOPLE BRING US
MONEY AND BE HAPPY DOING SO.
WE CAN DO IT.
5 MILLION GOLD.
WE CAN GET THE MONEY.
THERE'S NO DOUBT IN MY MIND.
[MARIELLE] HUH?
[SHORYU] HUH? UH?
(SHIMMER)
(TING)
[HENRIETTA] NOW IT'S TIME FOR
THE PLAN'S FIRST STAGE.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, MARIELLE,
I BROUGHT YOU A SNACK.
CHIEF NYAN‐TA MADE THIS
SANDWICH HIMSELF. UH...
[MARIELLE] I CAN'T DO IT.
STUPID UMEKO! I HATE HER!
I HATE HER! I HATE HER!
[NAOTSUGU] HO HO! HEY!
COME ON, NOW, EH‐
I HATE PAPERWORK,
THIS ROOM, EVERYTHING!
I WANT A BATH. I WANT TO GO
OUTSIDE. I WANT MY MOMMY!
[NAOTSUGU] OK, OK, MARIELLE.
I'LL JUST SET THIS, UH...
HERE YOU GO.
MMM.
MM! THIS IS GREAT!
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, MARIELLE...
[MARIELLE] HMM?
I THINK IT'S REALLY
GREAT YOU SIGNED OFF
ON SHIROE'S PLAN.
HUH?
[NAOTSUGU] IT WAS REALLY
SOMETHING SPECIAL TO HIM
THAT YOU DECIDED TO
HELP HIM OUT AND ALL.
SO, UH... SO THANKS A LOT.
[MARIELLE] OH... YOU'RE SUCH
A GOOD BOY, NAOTSUGU.
SUCH A GOOD BOY.
EASY, NOW.
YES, YOU ARE.
OH, YES, YOU ARE,
LITTLE NAOTSUGU.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE
HERE WITH SHIROE.
YEAH. NO BIG DEAL.
[NAOTSUGU] SO IT'S GOING
DOWN TOMORROW, HUH?
[MARIELLE]
YEAH, TOMORROW.
[DOLCHE] HEY, GUYS,
YOU WANT TO GET
SOMETHING TO MUNCH ON
BEFORE WE HEAD OUT TO
THE HUNTING GROUNDS?
[KAWARA]
YEAH, WHATEVER. I GUESS.
IT'S ALL GONNA BE
TASTELESS GARBAGE ANYWAY.
[ISAMI] IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU HAD TO REMIND US.
[KAWARA] WHAT'S THE DEAL?
THIS PLACE IS DESERTED.
[DOLCHE]
LIKE, WHERE
IS EVERYBODY?
[KAWARA] WELL, IF IT'S GONNA
BE BLAND, MIGHT AS WELL GET
THE CHEAPEST BLAND
IN TOWN, RIGHT?
[LYCOPENE YAWNS]
SO ARE YOU SMELLING
WHAT I'M SMELLING?
IT CAN'T BE.
[MARIELLE]
HELLO, RESIDENTS
OF AKIHABARA!
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO MISS
REAL FOOD, WE HAVE GOOD NEWS.
NOW YOU CAN BRING GENUINE
FLAVOR BACK TO YOUR TABLE.
THE CRESCENT MOON REFRESHMENT
STAND OPENS TODAY!
PLEASE, GIVE IT A TRY.
[SERARA]
AH! THANK YOU. THANK YOU
FOR YOUR PURCHASE! THANK YOU!
SERARA, HE HASN'T
EVEN ORDERED ANYTHING.
15 GOLD PIECES
FOR A CRESCENT BURGER,
18 GOLD FOR A CRISPY
CHICKEN STRIP BASKET,
AND 5 GOLD FOR A FREAKIN'
BLACK ROSE TEA?
[DOLCHE]
THAT'S PRETTY PRICEY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
[KAWARA] TOTALLY.
AND THEY'RE REALLY OVERDOING THE
HARD SELL.
[MARIELLE] HEY, MISTER,
[SMASH] HEY...
[MARIELLE] WOULD YOU CARE TO BE
THE FIRST AND TRY ONE OUT?
YOU'LL BE AMAZED AT HOW
YUMMY YUM‐YUM IT IS!
YEAH. SURE.
WHY NOT?
WHY DON'T YOU BRING OUT A
CRESCENT BURGER, SWEET CHEEKS,
FOR HER?
ARE YOU
KIDDING ME?
HA HA!
THANK YOU!
[MARIELLE] ONE CRESCENT
BURGER COMING RIGHT UP!
[ALL] THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[CUSTOMER 1] IT SMELLS SO GOOD.
[CUSTOMER 2] I'M NOT
BUYING THAT GREAT SMELL
IS GREAT TASTE.
[DOLCHE]
HMM, IT MAY LOOK GREAT,
BUT IT'S GONNA TASTE
LIKE TOTAL POOPY.
[MARIELLE]
GIVE IT A TRY.
(LYCOPENE SNIFFS)
[LYCOPENE] MM! MM!
[SMASH] WELL?
[LYCOPENE] OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD. MM!
IT‐IT TOTALLY TASTES
LIKE A FREAKIN' HAMBURGER.
[SMASH] HUH?!
[CUSTOMER 1] ALL RIGHT!
I WANT ONE!
[CUSTOMER 2] I WANT ONE, TOO!
[CUSTOMER 3]
YEAH, GIVE ME A BURGER,
SWEET CHEEKS.
[CUSTOMER 4] ME, TOO!
[DOLCHE] SAUCY, MEATY, JUICY,
AND SIMPLY FABULOUS!
[KAWARA]
IT'S FREAKING AWESOME.
[ISAMI] I CAN EAT, LIKE,
10 OF THESE THINGS.
[DOLCHE]
WE GOT TO TELL SOJI.
[CUSTOMER 1] I'LL TAKE
3 CRESCENT BURGERS...
[CUSTOMER 2]
5 CRISPY CHICKEN STRIPS.
[CLOAKED CUSTOMER] I'LL TAKE
ONE OF EVERYTHING ON THE MENU.
(CUSTOMERS ORDERING, INDISTINCT)
(WOOD RATTLING)
[SERARA] UM, UM, THIS IS
THE END OF THE LINE!
THANK YOU FOR STAYING IN
PLACE AND NOT SKIPPING AHEAD!
[ASUKA] WE ONLY HAVE
ONE BOX OF BURGERS LEFT!
[MARIELLE]
WHAT? REALLY?!
DON'T WORRY YOUR PRETTY
LITTLE HEAD, MARIELLE.
MORE BURGERS ARE ON
THEIR WAY RIGHT NOW.
[HENRIETTA] THIS IS WHERE WE
REALLY NEED TO GET GOING.
GET READY TO REALLY
CRANK THEM OUT!
[SOJIRO] WOW. THIS IS GOOD.
DO WE KNOW WHO MADE THIS?
HOW DID THEY DO IT?
[CUSTOMER 1] HAVE YOU TRIED
THE CRESCENT BURGER YET?
I HEARD IT'S FOOD THAT
ACTUALLY TASTES LIKE FOOD!
[CUSTOMER 2] YOU MEAN IT
DOESN'T TASTE LIKE DOG CRAP?
FOR REAL?
[KARASHIN] SUCH FLAVOR
AT THIS PRICE?
I WONDER WHAT IT'D TAKE TO GET
A PIECE OF THIS ACTION.
[KAYU] WE GOT TROUBLE, CHIEF!
YOU GOT TO SEE THIS!
[MICHITAKA] YOU'RE A LITTLE
LATE TO THE GAME, KAYU.
BUT, YES, IT'S GOOD.
MM! MM‐HMM.
[MICHITAKA] KEEP AN
EYE ON THAT SHOP.
FIND OUT WHO'S RUNNING
IT AND WHERE THEY GET
THEIR SUPPLIES FROM.
[MICHITAKA] I MEAN IT.
FIND OUT EVERYTHING YOU CAN.
[KAYU] RIGHT!
WILL DO, BOSS.
[MICHITAKA] NOW, THAT'S
A TASTY BURGER.
(BOAR GROWLING)
[NAOTSUGU] RIGHT. THAT
OUGHT TO DO US FOR NOW.
LET'S BOUNCE, OK?
COME ON.
[HIEN] YOU GOT IT.
[SHORYU] I'M GONNA GO HUNT
DOWN SOME MORE, ALL RIGHT?
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[SHORYU] YOU GUYS CAN
GO BACK IF YOU WANT.
[NAOTSUGU] DUDE, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO KILL YOURSELF.
SLOW AND STEADY
GETS THE PIG.
I AM NOT
GONNA LOSE.
HUH? LOSE WHAT, DUDE?
LET HIM GO AND KNOCK
HIMSELF OUT.
ARE YOU SURE
ABOUT THAT?
HE'S NOT LISTENING ANYWAY.
[SHORYU] I'M GOING.
FOR MY MARIELLE, ANYTHING.
(GROWLING)
[SHORYU]
HOLY CRAP!
A... A...
A GIANT BOAR...
[SHIROE] ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
REALLY GOOD WORK.
[MARIELLE] COME ON.
LIKE, COME ON!
LIKE, WHAT DID WE MAKE?
[HENRIETTA] WE EARNED
43,776 GOLD IN SALES.
THAT'S 1,159 CUSTOMERS
WHO SPENT AN AVERAGE OF
38 GOLD PIECES EACH.
[HENRIETTA] WE SOLD OUT THE
CRESCENT BURGERS WE PREPARED
AS WELL AS EVERYTHING ELSE,
EXCEPT THE BLACK ROSE TEA.
AWESOME! HA HA.
LIKE, THIS IS SO GREAT.
LIKE, WE OUGHT TO HAVE THAT
5 MILLION GOLD IN NO TIME IF
WE KEEP DOING THIS BUSINESS.
[SHIROE]
ACTUALLY, IT'S GONNA TAKE A LOT
MORE TIME THAN WE REALLY HAVE.
HUH? IT WILL?
[SHIROE] IT'D TAKE 120 MORE
DAYS BASED ON THOSE SALES.
AND 4 MONTHS IS
WAY TOO LONG.
[MARIELLE] THAT MIGHT BE,
BUT I KNOW WE, LIKE, TURNED
A LOT OF CUSTOMERS AWAY TODAY.
I COULD PROBABLY
SELL A LOT MORE.
LOOK, I KNOW WHERE
YOU'RE GOING WITH THIS.
I KNOW OUR POTENTIAL
CUSTOMER BASE.
[SHIROE] THERE ARE OVER 15,000
PLAYERS THAT WOULD EAT A
CRESCENT BURGER EVERY DAY.
[HENRIETTA] THE PROBLEM IS
NO MATTER HOW HIGH THE
DEMAND HAPPENS TO GROW,
WE CAN ONLY FEASIBLY SERVE
AROUND A THOUSAND CUSTOMERS
A DAY AND NOTHING MORE.
OUR GUILD JUST
ISN'T BIG ENOUGH.
(MARIELLE SIGHS)
THAT'S PRETTY
MUCH IT.
AND IF YOU REMEMBER,
MARIELLE,
THIS WASN'T ABOUT STAYING
IN BUSINESS AND MAKING MONEY.
OH, THAT'S
RIGHT! HA HA!
I GUESS ALL THOSE GOLD PIECES
WERE STARTING TO BLIND ME.
(LAUGHING)
I'LL JUST GO DEPOSIT EVERYTHING
WE EARNED TODAY IN THE BANK.
[SHIROE] THANKS.
[HENRIETTA] UH‐HUH.
[MARIELLE] OK, SHIROE, SINCE
WE CAN'T GET ALL THE MONEY
WITH THE CRESCENT BURGER,
DO WE DO YOUR OTHER PLAN?
YOU KNOW, SO, LIKE,
WE'LL HAVE ENOUGH.
[SHIROE]
OH, YEAH, IT'LL WORK.
BUT, LIKE, I REALLY
DON'T KNOW IF I CAN.
REMEMBER, HENRIETTA'S
GOT YOU COVERED ON
THE HARD PART.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
[HENRIETTA] YES.
LEAVE IT TO ME, OK?
IN EXCHANGE...
UH!
(HENRIETTA LAUGHING)
[HENRIETTA] WHERE DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE GOING?!
[AKATSUKI] OH, MY LORD HAS GIVEN
ME A SECRET MISSION TO EXECUTE!
DON'T TRY STOPPING ME! AH!
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE WAS KIND
ENOUGH TO LEND YOU TO ME.
ISN'T THAT JUST WONDERFUL?
MY LORD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU SOLD ME OUT AGAIN!
NOW, HURRY. PUT THIS ON!
[AKATSUKI] NO WAY!
I'M NOT SOME LITTLE DOLL
FOR YOU TO DRESS UP!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
[HENRIETTA] AH, AH, AH!
YOU CAN'T ENTER THAT ROOM.
[AKATSUKI]
WHAT'S THAT?
[HENRIETTA] THIS ZONE BELONGS TO
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE.
(BUZZING)
AND THAT WAREHOUSE ONLY
PERMITS GUILD MEMBERS.
AND I'M SORRY, SWEETIE,
BUT ARE YOU A GUILD MEMBER?
I GUESS I'LL
HAVE TO...
(BUZZING)
[AKATSUKI] ARE YOU
FREAKING KIDDING ME?
[HENRIETTA]
IT'S USELESS.
I SET IT SO THAT SKILLS
CAN'T BE USED HERE.
AND I CAN ALSO SET COMBAT
PERMISSIONS INDIVIDUALLY.
CLEVER, RIGHT?
(AKATSUKI WHIMPERING)
(SQUEALS)
[ASUKA, LILIANA, AND ASHLIN]
YOU'RE SO CUTE!
[NYAN‐TA] WELL, I'LL BE.
IT LOOKS ABSOLUTELY
FETCHING ON YOU.
DEAR GOD! I'M FREAKING
OUT ON THE CUTENESS!
HEY, HAVE ANY OF
YOU SEEN SHORYU?
[HENRIETTA] HM?
HE SHOULD HAVE
BEEN DONE ALREADY.
HE WANTED THE BIG
GAME, SO HE PROBABLY
ISN'T BACK YET.
LIKE, REALLY? I HOPE
HE'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
[RUMBLING]
OHH...
[LILIANA] OH, MY GOODNESS!
[ASUKA] UM, THERE'S A GIANT
BOAR STUCK IN THE HALLWAY.
[HIEN]
TH‐THAT'S A LOT OF PIG!
MISS MARIELLE, IS THIS
GONNA HELP THE KITCHEN ANY?
[SHORYU] UGH!
[MARIELLE] SHORYU! SHORYU!
(SHORYU BREATHING DEEPLY)
HE SAID HE HADN'T HAD
ANY SLEEP FOR A WHILE.
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
OH, POOR GUY.
[MARIELLE] THANKS FOR
YOUR HELP, EVERYONE.
COMPANIONS LIKE YOU
ARE REALLY A BLESSING.
[HIEN] FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH,
HE LOOKS HAPPY THAT WAY,
ALMOST DEAD OR NOT.
WELL, I HATE TO CAST
ASPERSIONS ON ALL
YOUR HARD WORK,
BUT THE FLAVOR OF A GIANT
BOAR IS ENTIRELY TOO
STRONG FOR WHAT WE DO.
(LAUGHTER)
[MARIELLE] SHH! YOU'RE GONNA
TOTALLY WAKE HIM UP.
[SHIROE]
EVERYONE IN CRESCENT MOON IS
SO FRIENDLY AND WELL‐MANNERED.
[SHIROE]
REALLY. THERE'S HENRIETTA
AND MARIELLE.
THEIR KINDNESS AND GLOWING
SMILES ARE INSPIRING
AND CONTAGIOUS.
ON TOP OF THAT, I FINALLY WENT
AND CREATED MY VERY OWN GUILD.
I'LL MAKE SURE YOU GET
TO MEET THEM SOON.
WE'RE GETTING
EVERYTHING READY.
JUST HAVE A LITTLE FAITH,
AND WE'LL GET THIS DONE.
(MINORI WHINCES)
[SHIROE]
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
I SWEAR IT.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
OH!
(SHIROE CLEARS THROAT)
[TOYA] SHIROE SAID THAT?
[MINORI] YEAH.
[TOYA]
WELL, ALL RIGHT, THEN.
[MINORI] IS IT OK?
[TOYA] HMM?
SERIOUSLY? IS ALL
THIS REALLY OK?
[SHIROE]
THIS IS STRANGE, CHIEF.
BACK WHEN I WAS PLAYING,
ALL OF THESE BUILDINGS
WERE BACKGROUND ART.
BUT NOW THE HUD SAYS THE
ZONES ARE ALL FOR SALE.
[NYAN‐TA]
IT SEEMS THAT WAY, HMM?
[SHIROE]
THAT'S NOT ALL EITHER.
EVERY CITY AND BUILDING IN
THE WORLD IS FOR SALE.
THE PRICES ARE JUST
OUTRAGEOUSLY HIGH.
[NYAN‐TA] AND IN LIGHT
OF THE FACT THAT YOU
NEED A SMALL FORTUNE
TO BUY A BUILDING
AROUND HERE,
MAYBE TOKYO STATION SHOULD
BE OUR HEADQUARTERS, HMM?
[SHIROE] NOT QUITE.
(OWL HOOTING)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
[SOJIRO]
YOU GUYS WAIT LONG?
MASTER SHIROE, MASTER NYAN‐TA,
IT'S BEEN QUITE A WHILE.
[SHIROE] HEY, SOJIRO.
[NYAN‐TA] HEY, LITTLE MAN.
I HEARD YOU WENT AND STARTED
YOUR OWN GUILD, HMM?
[SOJIRO] YUP. IT'S CALLED
THE BRIGADE OF THE WEST WIND.
[SHIROE] IT'S SMALL,
BUT SOJIRO'S BRIGADE
OF THE WEST WIND
IS JUST AS POWERFUL AS THE
BIGGEST GUILDS OUT THERE.
[NYAN‐TA] MEOW?
[SOJIRO] NOT REALLY.
WE WERE JUST GETTING OUR
FEET WET STARTING THE GUILD.
THEN THE APOCALYPSE CAME AROUND
AND REWROTE ALL OUR PRIORITIES.
I HONESTLY HADN'T BEEN KEEPING
UP WITH THINGS AS MUCH
OR LOGGING IN AS OFTEN
SINCE THE TEA PARTY BROKE UP.
ARE YOU STILL KEEPING
COMPANY WITH THAT DELIGHTFUL
NAZNA AND MISS SAKI?
YEAH! NAZNA'S IN MY GUILD.
AND SHE'S JUST AS EASYGOING
AS SHE EVER WAS.
SAKI WAS ALSO IN
THE GUILD WITH US,
BUT I GUESS SHE DIDN'T LOG
IN DURING THE DAY OF
THE APOCALYPSE.
SO WHILE I'M STILL
THINKING ABOUT IT,
WOULD YOU HAPPEN
TO BE A...
ARE YOU STILL AS POPULAR WITH
THE GIRLS AS YOU USED TO BE?
[SOJIRO] HA HA. AH,
COME ON. I DON'T KNOW.
[NYAN‐TA] AH! TO BE
YOUNG AGAIN. HA HA.
[SOJIRO] SO TELL ME
SOMETHING, SHIROE,
YOU FINALLY CALLED.
WHAT INSPIRED YOU
TO GET IN TOUCH?
[SHIROE]
WELL, YOU SEE‐
[SOJIRO]
I GUESS WHAT
I MEAN IS,
I THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T LIKE
ME OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[SOJIRO]
BECAUSE, WELL, I REMEMBER
ASKING YOU TO JOIN ME,
BUT THEN YOU KIND OF
SAID "NO," YOU KNOW?
[SHIROE] YEAH, BUT
IT WASN'T LIKE THAT.
I LIKE YOU FINE, SOJIRO.
I JUST DIDN'T FEEL
LIKE SPENDING ALL THAT
TIME BEING INVOLVED
WITH A GUILD
BACK THEN.
[SHIROE]
BUT HERE'S THE THING.
THE APOCALYPSE MADE THIS
PLACE OUR REAL WORLD.
AND SO THE WAY
WE LIVE HERE IS
GOING TO BE DIFFERENT
THAN IT WAS WHEN
IT WAS JUST A GAME.
[SHIROE] I CHOSE TO USE THE
POWER I HAVE TO PROTECT
PEOPLE WHO DON'T.
I HAVE MADE A
GUILD OF MY OWN.
WE'RE STARTING OUT,
AND WE'RE KIND OF SMALL.
BUT IT'S NOT A BAD THING
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
BUT I'LL ONLY HAVE
A PLACE FOR MYSELF
AFTER I'VE GIVEN OTHER
PEOPLE THE CHANCE.
I THINK THAT'S FAIR.
OH.
SO THAT BRINGS ME BACK
TO WHY YOU CALLED ME.
[NYAN‐TA]
WELL, MY FRIEND,
WHAT WE WANT AT THE
MOMENT IS YOUR OPINION
OF AKIHABARA, HMM?
[SOJIRO]
AH. IT'S LIKE A...
A PRISON.
HONESTLY?
[SOJIRO] IT'S NOT
JUST AKIHABARA.
DEPENDING ON HOW YOU
LOOK AT IT, THE WHOLE
WORLD'S A PRISON.
I MEAN, YOU CAN'T
EVEN DIE HERE.
[SHIROE]
WELL, I KNOW WE CAN FIX IT.
AND I NEED YOUR HELP.
YEAH, I'M IN.
HUH. YOU SURE?
DON'T YOU WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
WHAT YOU'RE AGREEING TO FIRST?
[SOJIRO] I DON'T THINK
THAT'LL BE NECESSARY.
I JUST HAVE A FEELING IT'S
GONNA WORK OUT SOMEHOW.
A SAMURAI'S JOB IS TO
FIGHT ON THE FRONT LINES
REGARDLESS OF THE PLAN.
PLUS, BACK IN OUR TEA PARTY
DAYS, OUR STRATEGISTS ALWAYS
SEEMED TO COME UP WITH SOMETHING
AMAZING TO GET US THROUGH.
SOJIRO...
[NYAN‐TA] YOU'RE ONE OF THE
GOOD ONES, LITTLE MAN.
ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
[SOJIRO] COME ON,
YOU GUYS. HA HA!
I GOT MORE
BURGER MEAT HERE.
[CUSTOMER]
3 CRESCENT BURGERS.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
LET ME COME AROUND AND GET
YOUR ORDER WHILE YOU WAIT.
YOU'RE SO CUTE!
OH, PLEASE ADD ME
TO YOUR FRIENDS' LIST.
HEY, HOLD YOUR HORSES. HE SAID
HE WAS GONNA COME TO YOU.
SERIOUSLY, BOSS?
ARE YOU REALLY JUST GONNA
SIT OUT HERE ALL DAY LONG
HOCKING BURGERS FOR
THIS SHIROE FELLA?
[SOJIRO]
OF COURSE NOT.
THERE'S A LOT MORE
TO IT THAN THIS.
I HAVE FAITH IN HIS PLAN.
I KNOW HE CAN MAKE THIS RIGHT.
[SHIROE] NOW THEN, TIME FOR
THE PLAN'S SECOND STAGE.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
MICHITAKA OF THE MARINE AGENCY.
KARASHIN OF SHOPPING STREET 8.
RODERICK OF THE RODERICK
MERCHANT GUILD.
MASTERS OF THE LARGEST CRAFTING
GUILDS GATHER INTO ONE PLACE.
THEIR TRADING PARTNERS
ARE THE CRESCENT MOONS,
MARIELLE AND HENRIETTA.
AND THE SHADOW THAT
MANIPULATES THEM?
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.