[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IN OUR NEW WORLD,
IN ADDITION TO ADVENTURERS
AND PEOPLE OF THE LAND,
THERE ARE ALSO GROUPS
CALLED DEMI‐HUMANS.
FOR EXAMPLE, THE GOBLINS.
THEY HAVE LIMITED INTELLIGENCE
BUT ARE HARDY AND BREED QUICKLY.
AND ABOVE ALL,
THEY'RE CRUEL AND WICKED.
(GOBLIN HISSES)
AN INDIVIDUAL GOBLIN IS NO MATCH
FOR AN ADVENTURER OF EVEN
INTERMEDIATE STRENGTH.
HOWEVER, THEIR NUMBERS
AND VARIETY SHOULD NOT
BE UNDERESTIMATED.
YOU CAN FIND MOST GOBLINS
IN THE NORTHEAST PART
OF THE ISLAND CHAIN.
[SHIROE] OBVIOUSLY,
SOME OF THESE CONFLICT.
AND IT WOULD PROBABLY BE
REALLY BAD FORM ON OUR PART
IF WE SHOW UP AT
ONLY ONE OF THESE.
[KRUSTY] THERE'S THE
BANQUET WITH LORD DALTE,
THE EVENING PARTY WITH MOSTLY
YOUNG KNIGHTS ATTENDING,
AND A DINNER MEETING WITH
COUNT KIRINO OF TSUKUBA
AND THE ACADEMICS GUILD.
YEAH, I'D BE OUT OF MY LEAGUE
WITH THAT ACADEMICS GUILD.
[KRUSTY] SAME HERE.
ACADEMICS. MY KIND OF PEOPLE.
AND SO, WHY DON'T YOU
GO SEE THE KNIGHTS, KRUSTY?
I'M SURE THE DANCE
WILL AGREE WITH YOU.
[KRUSTY] THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD IDEA, ACTUALLY.
RIGHT. LOOKS LIKE I'LL TAKE
THE BANQUET WITH LORD DALTE.
(AKATSUKI GROWLING)
[HENRIETTA] YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO BE OK, KRUSTY?
YOU DO REALIZE THAT YOU'LL BE
SPENDING MOST OF YOUR TIME
FLATTERING LORDS
AND NOBLE LADIES?
[KRUSTY] LATELY, I FOUND A
SHIELD FOR ALL MY SHORTCOMINGS
THAT'S SO EFFECTIVE,
IT'S NEARLY UNBREAKABLE.
I'LL BE BETTER
THAN OK, THANK YOU.
[ALL] A SHIELD?
(YAWNING)
(DOOR OPENS)
[ELISSA] IT'S ALMOST BEDTIME,
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
(RAYNESHIA SIGHS)
UH, NO, ELISSA.
I'M NOT WEARING
THOSE SILK PAJAMAS.
THOSE PAJAMAS ARE EVIL.
ARE YOU REALLY GOING
TO DO THIS AGAIN?
[ELISSA] YOUR FLANNELS, MILADY.
(RAYNESHIA SQUEALS)
THESE ARE PERFECT, AND I KNEW
YOU WERE GONNA BRING THEM!
THANK YOU!
[ELISSA] YOU NEED TO WEAR THE
SILK EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE.
I'M THE ONE WHO'S
GETTING YELLED AT.
[RAYNESHIA] SURE,
EVENTUALLY.
(ELISSA SIGHS)
YOU DO KNOW THAT ALL THE
GENTLEMEN IN MAIHAMA
REFER TO YOU AS THE MELANCHOLY
TWILIGHT PRINCESS?
WELL, A REAL GENTLEMAN WOULDN'T
SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
AND I AM, BY MY OWN
ADMISSION, UNMOTIVATED.
[ELISSA] WELL, I DOUBT ANY OF
THEM WOULD APPRECIATE YOU
LOUNGING AROUND IN YOUR
SLEEPWEAR ALL DAY.
YEAH. WHATEVER.
[KRUSTY] I'M SORRY, LORD KILIVA,
BUT I ACTUALLY HAVE OTHER
PLANS FOR TONIGHT.
[KILIVA] HUH? DO YOU
HAVE ANOTHER ENGAGEMENT?
OH. PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
UH...
IT IS A PLEASURE TO
MEET YOU, MILADY.
I'M THE ADVENTURER
THEY CALL KRUSTY.
PLEASED TO MAKE
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
[RAYNESHIA] OK. SO WHAT DID
YOU MEAN BY "YOUR PLANS"?
[KRUSTY] THAT WAS TO
GET RID OF MY SHADOW.
I'M SORRY IF IT CAUSED YOU
ANY DISTRESS, OF COURSE.
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
HE'S NOT A BAD GUY, PER SE,
BUT HE IS ANNOYING.
YOU WERE JUST THINKING ABOUT
HOW ANNOYING I AM, RIGHT?
[RAYNESHIA] UH! UH...
[KRUSTY] AND I'M SURE THAT WHEN
OUR EYES FIRST MET, YOU THOUGHT,
"HE'S GONNA BOTHER ME,
ISN'T HE?"
[RAYNESHIA] UHH!
H‐H‐HOW DID YOU...?
WELL, LET'S SAY IT'S
A LITTLE GIFT I HAVE.
UH...
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
HE CAN READ MY MIND.
[KRUSTY] CARE TO
JOIN ME FOR TEA?
ALL THESE LORDS HAVE BEEN
RUNNING ME RAGGED ALL DAY.
[RAYNESHIA] WELL, I, UH‐‐
[KRUSTY] I REALIZE THE
PROSPECT DOESN'T PLEASE YOU,
BUT RIGHT NOW,
ME AND MY FRIENDS ARE REALLY
UNDER THE MAGNIFYING GLASS.
OH.
[KRUSTY] IF THE TWO OF US
WERE TO TAKE TEA TOGETHER,
IT MIGHT ACTUALLY PROVIDE
BOTH OF US AN EXCUSE
TO SKIP SOME OF THE EVENTS
OTHER PEOPLE HAVE PLANNED.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
(SHUDDERING) OH, MY!
YOU ARE BAD, MR. BAD PERSON.
[ELISSA] PLEASE BE CAREFUL
AROUND HIM, PRINCESS.
OH, YES, HE'S A BAD MAN WHO CAN
TELL EXACTLY WHAT I'M THINKING.
NAUGHTY BOY.
[ELISSA] THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
HUH?
[ELISSA] HE'S AN ADVENTURER,
AND REALLY WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE LIKE.
[RAYNESHIA] HMM... YEAH.
[ELISSA] YOU KNOW I DON'T
WANT TO REMIND YOU OF THIS,
SINCE IT'S SUCH
A BOTHER FOR YOU,
BUT YOU HAVE TO CONSIDER
YOUR POSITION AS A MEMBER OF
THE DUKE'S FAMILY, AFTER ALL.
RIGHT...
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
A DUCAL FAMILY MEMBER?
POTENTIAL DUCHESS?
(SIGHING)
BEYOND BEAUTIFUL
AS ALWAYS.
JUST SIMPLY
DELICATE, YES.
[ALL] HMM?
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
TAKE IT EASY, GENTLEMEN.
MY GRANDFATHER ISN'T AROUND
TO HEAR YOUR EMPTY COMPLIMENTS.
(SIGHING)
ANYONE CAN BE BEAUTIFUL AND
DELICATE WITH THE RIGHT
BAUBLES AND BEADS,
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU'RE NOT
ALLOWED TO DRESS YOURSELF.
HOW LONG IS THIS GOING TO GO ON?
(SHOUTING, SWORDS CLANGING)
HUH?
UH...
HMM.
[KNIGHT] YAA! YA!
YAA!
UH... UH...
OHH.
[KNIGHT] TH‐THE MATCH IS YOURS.
I DON'T BELIEVE I'VE BEEN
HIT THAT HARD BEFORE
IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
I'D BE HONORED TO BE YOUR
APPRENTICE, IF YOU'D HAVE ME.
(NERVOUS LAUGH)
[RAYNESHIA] A GOODWILL MATCH?
[KRUSTY] YES. THEY INVITED ME.
THAT'S KIND OF
SURPRISING.
WHAT IS, MILADY?
WOULDN'T AN ADVENTURER
LIKE YOU FIND SOMETHING
LIKE THIS TEDIOUS?
[KRUSTY] NOT AT ALL.
[RAYNESHIA] UH...
[KRUSTY] I'D REALLY LIKE
TO KNOW MORE ABOUT THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND,
AND THIS IS A
GREAT OPPORTUNITY.
(CHEERING)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
THAT'S A LIE.
HE'S LOOKING TO SEE HOW
SKILLED OUR FIGHTERS ARE.
HUH?
[SHIROE] KRUSTY?
[SCHOLAR] OOH, THAT'S
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
(KNIGHT LAUGHS)
[RAYNESHIA] SO, AS AN
ADVENTURER,
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF
YOUR SPARRING MATCHES?
IT'S NOT LIKE ANY OF THEM
COULD BE STRONGER THAN YOU.
[KRUSTY] NO, THEY WERE
ALL VERY TALENTED.
THAT LAST FIGHT
WAS RATHER CLOSE.
I SEE.
[KRUSTY] SO IT WOULDN'T BE
EASY TO FIGHT YOUR WAY UP
AND EARN FIRST RANK HERE.
HMM.
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA?
[KNIGHTS] HUH?
[RAYNESHIA] HUH? UH, YES?
[KRUSTY] IF IT PLEASES YOU,
WOULD YOU OFFER A REWARD
TO THE STRONGEST OF THESE
BRAVE KNIGHTS WHO ARE FIGHTING
FOR YOUR AMUSEMENT TODAY?
[RAYNESHIA] A REWARD?
A SIMPLE REWARD...
THE RIGHT TO ACCOMPANY
YOU TO TONIGHT'S PARTY.
(CHEERING)
(CRINGING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
WELL, I'LL BE. THAT'S A
PRETTY GOOD SHIELD, KRUSTY.
[LORD 1] SO WHAT DOES THE
DUKE INTEND TO DO WITH
THE ADVENTURERS
NOW THAT THEY'RE HERE?
[LORD 2] HE'S GOT THEM
AT THE TABLE, BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU CAN TALK TO THEM.
[LORD 1] BY THE WAY,
HAVE ANY OF YOUR PEOPLE HEARD
WHERE THE IZUMO KNIGHTS ARE?
[LORD 2] WE CAN JUST HIRE
ADVENTURERS TO FIND THAT OUT.
HMM.
[LORD 2] IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU CAN KILL ANY OF THEM.
OHH.
GOOD AFTERNOON, GENTLEMEN.
HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
THERE SHE IS!
[BOY] HIDE‐AND‐SEEK GENIUS!
[GIRL] YOU HAVE TO COME
PLAY WITH US AGAIN, OK?
[KIDS] WHOA!
[BOY] SHE'S THE BEST
HIDE‐AND‐SEEKER EVER!
I AM NOT PLAYING
HIDE‐AND‐SEEK.
UGH!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT
YOUR THEORY IMPLIES THAT
PEOPLE OF THE LAND CAN'T EVOLVE
BEYOND WHERE THEY ARE?!
AND YOUR REFUSAL TO ACCEPT
MY THEORY IS HINDERING
THESE DISCUSSIONS, YOU IDIOT!
WE MIGHT NEED TO
DEFINE "EVOLUTION."
THERE'S NO POINT IN DEBATING
IT UNTIL WE HAVE A FIRM
IDEA OF WHAT IT IS.
I GUESS I WAS EXPECTING
SOMETHING MORE CALM AND
COLLECTED OUT OF THESE GUYS.
(ARGUING CONTINUES)
(RINGING)
HUH?
[MINORI] UM, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] MINORI?
[MINORI]I'M HEADING BACK TO
THE DUNGEON IN A LITTLE BIT.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE SOME
TIME TO TALK A WHILE?
[SHIROE] OH, SORRY.
I‐I'M SORT OF RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF A CONFERENCE.
[MINORI]
HUH? OH, MY GOODNESS! I'M SORRY!
I'LL BE FINE. I'LL JUST
TALK TO YOU LATER, OK?
HMM... HMM.
HMM.
(KNIGHTS CHEER)
[GIRLS] OOH! GO!
[KNIGHT] YOW!
OHH!
(GIRLS GASP)
(GROANING)
(CHEERING)
[GIRLS] AWESOME!
(APPLAUSE)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] WELL, OF
COURSE HE WAS GOING TO WIN.
HUH?
HMM.
(NERVOUS GIGGLE)
(BIRDS CHIRP)
[KRUSTY] FACING SO MANY
OF YOUR FINEST YOUNG AND
RENOWNED KNIGHTS IS TIRING.
WAS THAT SARCASM?
[KRUSTY] OF COURSE NOT.
[RAYNESHIA] HMM.
[KRUSTY] HMM.
[RAYNESHIA] UH...
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[KRUSTY] WAKE ME UP IN
A WHILE, IF YOU WOULD?
UH, WHAT IF SOMEONE SEES
YOU LYING DOWN LIKE THAT?
[KRUSTY] DON'T CARE. I'M ONLY
A BARBARIC ADVENTURER.
I'M SURE THE LORDS
WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED IF
THEY SAW ME DOING THIS.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
WELL, THAT'S HARDLY FAIR.
[KRUSTY] AND YOU'RE PROBABLY
THINKING IT ISN'T FAIR.
UH!
YOU COULD ALWAYS JOIN ME.
THE TABLE'S COOL, AND THERE'S
ROOM FOR BOTH OF US HERE.
[RAYNESHIA] OH...
(CHIRPING)
HMM...
[LORD 1] SO YOU'RE
SAYING THAT'S IT?
[LORD 2] OH, YES,
MOST DEFINITELY.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
HMM.
[KRUSTY] ADVENTURERS ARE FREE.
[RAYNESHIA] THEY'RE FREE?
[KRUSTY] WE EAT
WHENEVER WE WANT,
SLEEP WHEN WE FEEL LIKE IT,
AND MOVE PRETTY MUCH
WHEREVER WE PLEASE.
HOWEVER, YOU HAVE TO
WANT IT AND WORK FOR IT.
[RAYNESHIA] FREEDOM.
(RUNNING)
(PANTING)
AH!
(BONES RATTLING)
(PANTING)
LOOK! OVER THERE!
UGH!
[SERARA] OHH...
[ISUZU] HMM...
(GULPING)
(SIGHS)
IT'S ONLY BEEN AN HOUR
AND WE'RE RUNNING AGAIN.
(ALL SIGH)
[RUDY] WE'VE DONE
THIS OVER AND OVER.
WHY CAN'T WE WIN?!
I'M GETTING HURT IN THERE
BECAUSE YOU GUYS DON'T
KNOW HOW TO HEAL.
YOU HEALERS NEED TO STEP IT UP!
[TOYA] THAT'S JUST
ABOUT ENOUGH OUT OF YOU!
EVERYONE'S DOING THE
BEST THAT THEY CAN!
SO THEN WHY DOES THIS
KEEP HAPPENING TO US?
WHY AM I SO WEAK?
I MEAN, I'VE GONE
UP TO LEVEL 24.
THE ENEMIES RANGE FROM 17 TO 21.
SO WHAT THE HECK
IS SO HARD ABOUT IT?!
WE SHOULD BE DOING BETTER!
SERIOUSLY, GUYS,
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
WELL, IT'S BECAUSE...
[ALL] HUH?
[TOYA] LOOK, RUNDELL,
YOU'RE NOT FIGHTING
TO YOUR FULL POTENTIAL.
(RUDY GRUMBLES)
SO YOU'RE SAYING THAT IT'S ME.
IT'S MY FAULT...
[MARIELLE] OH, MY GOD.
WILL THOSE KIDS BE OK?
IT'S BEEN 4 DAYS OR SOMETHING
SINCE THEY ENTERED THE DUNGEON.
[NAOTSUGU] SERIOUSLY,
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
CHILL. YA!
[MARIELLE] BUT WHAT IF SOMETHING
HAPPENS AND THEY GET SENT
BACK TO AKIHABARA?
[NAOTSUGU] THEN WE'LL
JUST USE OUR GRIFFINS
TO GET THEM BACK.
YOU TALK LIKE IT'S
NOT YOUR PROBLEM.
[NAOTSUGU] WELL, THEY SAY
LIONS TOSS THEIR CUBS
OFF CLIFFS, RIGHT?
(KIDS CHEER)
[MARIELLE] OH, THAT ISN'T TRUE.
[NAOTSUGU] IT IS TOO!
YOU WON'T BEAT THE DUNGEON
TEAMS WITH THAT STUFF.
YOU GOT TO THINK BIGGER!
[NAOTSUGU] EITHER WAY,
BEING AN OVERPROTECTIVE
NINNY AIN'T GONNA HELP.
THE POINT OF THIS TRAINING
CAMP IS TO HELP THESE LITTLE
FARTS GAIN EXPERIENCE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OK, I GOT IT. I GUESS I'LL
BELIEVE IN THEM, THEN.
[MARIELLE] WELL, I THINK I'LL
GO, LIKE, EAT SOME CRAB.
(MARIELLE GIGGLES)
THANKS!
TAKE CARE, NOW!
(NYANTA HUMS)
THOSE BIG ONES
DON'T HAVE ANY FLAVOR.
[NAOTSUGU] IT'S GOOD!
THE NEW KIDS GET TRAINING, AND I
GET TO EAT SOME YUMMY SEAFOOD!
TWO BIRDS WITH ONE STONE!
HUH?
(WIND BLOWING)
[MARIELLE] SHORYU, WHAT'S THAT
STUFF OVER THERE?
[SHORYU] I DON'T KNOW.
LOOKS LIKE BUBBLES.
[MARIELLE] THEY DISAPPEARED!
[SHORYU] WHAT WAS THAT?
[DALTE] SO HOW
DO YOU LIKE IT?
THIS MEAT HAS BEEN TOUTED AS THE
VERY BEST IN ALL OF MY DOMAIN.
MMM.
[MICHITAKA] IT'S DELICIOUS,
YOUR LORDSHIP.
I'VE SENT FOR SOME CHEFS
FROM MY OWN GUILD.
NEXT TIME WE GET TOGETHER,
IT WILL HAVE TO BE MY TREAT.
I LOOK FORWARD TO THAT.
I'VE HEARD MANY RUMORS ABOUT
THE AKIHABARAN COOKING STYLE.
THIS REVOLUTION HAS GREATLY
AFFECTED OUR EATING HABITS
AND WHAT WE CONSIDER
TANTALIZING TO OUR PALATES.
EVERYONE'S IN LOVE
WITH THE NEW FOOD.
THE PEOPLE ARE MORE MOTIVATED
TO FIND AND CREATE THAT
GOOD FOOD, AS WELL.
WHY, THE EFFECT THIS PHENOMENON
HAS HAD ON PRODUCTIVITY ALONE
IS POSITIVELY AMAZING.
AH.
[DALTE] EVERYTHING FROM
THE AMOUNT OF CARE WE TAKE
ON THE FARMS HARVESTING
AND TRANSPORTING PRODUCE AND
MEATS TO MARKET HAS CHANGED.
[MICHITAKA] THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
[DALTE] WE DO STILL HAVE
ONE NAGGING PROBLEM, HOWEVER.
OH, YEAH?
[DALTE] RAISING THIS NEW
TASTY FOOD AND SHARING
IT ACROSS THE COUNTRY
TO AS MANY MARKETS AS WE CAN
DELIGHTS A GREAT MANY PEOPLE.
AND OF COURSE, THIS HAS
BENEFITED OUR DOMAIN IN THE
FORM OF AMAZING NEW PROFITS.
HOWEVER, TRANSPORTING IT OVER
THE LAND TENDS TO INVITE...
[MICHITAKA] ...MONSTERS, RIGHT?
[DALTE] INDEED...
AND SO I HAVE A REQUEST,
GUILD MASTER MICHITAKA.
YOU WANT US TO FIGHT
OFF SOME GOBLINS.
NOT EXACTLY. WE HAD
SOMETHING A LITTLE LESS
VIOLENT TO ASK OF YOU.
[MICHITAKA] HMM?
HMM. WE'RE SEEKING MARITIME
TRANSPORT KNOW‐HOW.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
[LORD] PRINCESS RAYNESHIA'S
SAD EXPRESSION...
SHE MUST BE TROUBLED BY
THE WORLD'S FUTURE.
I FEEL FOR HER.
[KRUSTY] I KNOW IT'S
A BOTHER TO YOU...
BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO SMILE
AT LEAST A LITTLE BIT.
I KNOW IT HAS TO BE ANNOYING
TO YOU, ALL THAT FLATTERY.
I'VE ONLY BEEN HERE A
LITTLE WHILE, AND I KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT IT'S LIKE.
[RAYNESHIA] I‐I REALLY
DON'T THINK YOU DO. HMM.
[KRUSTY] OH...HUH.
[GIRL 1] PRINCESS RAYNESHIA?
I'M SO SORRY TO INTERRUPT.
IT MUST SEEM AWFULLY
FORWARD OF US.
[GIRL 2] MAY WE JOIN YOU?
WE'D LOVE TO CHAT.
[GIRL 1] WE BROUGHT COOKIES!
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
THESE GIRLS ARE NICE ENOUGH
AND ALL, BUT... UGH.
WE SAW YOU
FIGHT OUT THERE.
WHAT YOU DID WITH YOUR
SWORD WAS REALLY AMAZING.
YOU'RE REALLY STRONG,
AREN'T YOU?
[KRUSTY] NO. I STILL
HAVE A LONG WAY TO GO.
OH, DON'T
BE SO MODEST.
YOU WERE SO GOOD,
YOU TOOK MY BREATH AWAY.
[KRUSTY] I'M UNWORTHY OF PRAISE
FROM LADIES AS LOVELY AS YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] GREAT.
WHY IS HE SO POLITE AND FUN WITH
THEM AND A COMPLETE SNOT TO ME?
KRUSTY, YOU'RE
JUST SO AWESOME!
OF ALL THE ADVENTURERS,
YOU'RE THE MOST COOL,
NOBLE, AND HANDSOME!
YEAH. EVERYBODY'S
BEEN TALKING
ABOUT YOU, KRUSTY.
EMBARRASSED AND FLATTERED
AT THE SAME TIME.
[GIRL 1] NO, NO.
IT'S SO OBVIOUS THAT YOUR
HANDSOME, DIGNIFIED ELEGANCE
IS WHY THE PRINCESS HAS LETTING
YOU BE AROUND HER TONIGHT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT,
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA?
[RAYNESHIA] UH, YES, ABSOLUTELY!
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
AND WHAT DID I JUST AGREE TO?
[GIRL 1] PRINCESS RAYNESHIA
IS SO BEAUTIFUL,
IT'S A PRIVILEGE
JUST BEING WITH HER.
[KRUSTY] SHE'S VERY KIND
AND COMPASSIONATE.
SHE'D HAVE TO BE TO LET A
BARBARIAN LIKE ME STAY IN
HER COMPANY FOR VERY LONG.
UHH... UHH...
[KRUSTY] ESPECIALLY SINCE
I'M NOT FAMILIAR WITH
THE MANNERS OF THE COURT.
HER KIND SOLICITATIONS ALLOW ME
TO AVOID BEING LOOKED UPON
AS A COMPLETE PHILISTINE.
IT IS AN HONOR OF
WHICH I AM UNWORTHY.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] AH...
OH, MR. BAD PERSON,
YOU ARE BAD...
THE WORST BAD PERSON EVER!
OH, COME ON! WE'VE
GOT TO INTRODUCE YOU
AROUND TO EVERYBODY!
AND ONCE EVERYONE IN THE
COURT GETS TO KNOW YOU,
I'M SURE THEY WON'T THINK YOU'RE
A PHILA‐WHATCHAMACALLIT.
[KRUSTY] NO. I'M A BARBARIAN
WHO KNOWS ONLY WAR.
AND UNTIL I CAN REPAY
THE PRINCESS FOR THE
KINDNESS SHE'S SHOWN ME,
I SIMPLY CANNOT LEAVE HER SIDE.
[GIRLS] OHH!
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
YOUR EVIL KNOWS
NO BOUNDS, DOES IT?
[GIRL 1] OH, A KNIGHT
SERVING HIS LADY!
[GIRL 2] IT'S SO SWEET!
[RAYNESHIA] LEAVE IF YOU WANT.
IF THE PRETTY PALACE FLOWERS
HAVE YOUR ATTENTION,
DON'T LET ME STOP YOU
FROM TAKING OFF.
TA.
[KRUSTY] I'M AFRAID I
ALREADY HAVE MY HANDS
FULL WITH ONE FLOWER.
STUFFING HER FACE.
OH, RIGHT. I GUESS I DON'T NEED
TO TELL YOU ABOUT GIRLS, DO I?
[KRUSTY] DEPENDS
ON THE GIRL.
[RAYNESHIA] OH... HUH?
[KRUSTY] I HAVE A LITTLE SISTER
BACK WHERE I COME FROM.
SHE'S GOT A LOT OF PRINCESS
IN HER, IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
[RAYNESHIA] UH, SO YOU'RE
SAYING THAT I'M KIND OF
LIKE YOUR SISTER?
YEAH.
YOU CAN'T SEE HER RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T GET HOME?
BOTH WOULD DEFINITELY BE
A CHALLENGE FOR ME.
YOU REALLY MISS HER,
THEN, DON'T YOU?
[KRUSTY] I COULDN'T SAY.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
YOU'RE LYING AGAIN.
[KRUSTY] YOU REMIND ME
OF HER QUITE A BIT...
YOU CATCHING A NAP ON A TABLE,
EVEN THOUGH IT ISN'T LADY‐LIKE.
UHH...
[KRUSTY] SHE'D LAY AROUND
THE HOUSE ALL DAY IF YOU
DIDN'T GET HER UP,
AND FORGET ANY OF
THOSE FANCY TALKS.
[RAYNESHIA] HEY, YOU DON'T
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT ME!
HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY SAY THAT?
[KRUSTY] BECAUSE YOU'RE
EXACTLY LIKE SHE IS.
[RAYNESHIA] UHH...
[KRUSTY] IT'S AMAZING, REALLY.
BEING AROUND YOU HAS
SOMEHOW MADE THIS WHOLE
AFFAIR A LOT EASIER ON ME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
GIVE ME A CHANCE TO PAY YOU
BACK DURING THE CONFERENCE?
ONE HAND WASHES THE OTHER, HUH?
[KRUSTY] TIT FOR TAT.
[RAYNESHIA]
ALL RIGHT. IT'S A DEAL.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
KISS MY HAND, DUMMY!
HMM.
(WALTZ MUSIC PLAYING)
UH...
[AKATSUKI]
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3...
AKATSUKI. YOU'RE AWAKE?
(AKATSUKI GASPS)
MY LORD... HOW LONG
WERE YOU THERE?!
NOT LONG. YOU THIRSTY?
(AKATSUKI CRINGES)
[SHIROE] HERE YOU GO.
THE GUYS FROM THE ACADEMIC
GUILD FINALLY LET ME GO.
THEY KEPT PESTERING
ME TO LET THEM DO
RESEARCH ON ADVENTURERS.
[AKATSUKI] OK...
HMM.
AKATSUKI, THINKING:
HIS HAIR SWIRLS TO
THE RIGHT. IT'S CUTE.
[SHIROE] SO, DID YOU
LEARN ANYTHING NEW?
[AKATSUKI] WELL...
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND SEE
US AS POTENTIAL ENEMIES,
BUT THEY DON'T SEEM TO BE
PLANNING ANYTHING TO HURT US.
THEY JUST HAVE THEIR WORRIES.
[SHIROE] I GUESS
THAT'S GOOD.
I THINK WHAT FRIGHTENS THEM
THE MOST IS OUR POWER, MY LORD.
NEITHER OF US HAS A REAL
GOOD IDEA AS TO WHAT THE
OTHER IS TRULY CAPABLE OF.
SO THEY EITHER REALLY LIKE US
OR THEY'RE GONNA KILL US ALL.
WAS THERE ANYTHING ELSE?
LET ME THINK...
I OVERHEARD SOMETHING ABOUT
THE IZUMO KNIGHTS BEING MISSING.
[SHIROE] "IZUMO KNIGHTS"?
(GASPS)
(RUMBLING)
(RUMBLING STOPS)
[MAN] HELLO. YOU MUST BE
SHIROE OF LOG HORIZON.
I APOLOGIZE FOR MY RATHER
DRAMATIC ENTRANCE,
BUT I HAVE COME TO SPEAK
WITH YOU THIS EVENING.
AND YOU ARE...?
I'M THE MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE.
REGAN IS MY NAME.
WE HAVE MUCH TO DISCUSS.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
THAT DAY, EVERYTHING CHANGED.
THAT DAY, I SUDDENLY
FOUND MYSELF HERE.
THAT DAY, THE APOCALYPSE
DESCENDED ON TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
THE MAGE OF ETERNAL EYES, REGAN,
SPEAKS REGARDING ITS SECRETS.
SHIROE LEARNS THE RULES THAT
GOVERN THE LIVES OF ADVENTURERS.
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.