[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] DUNGEONS
ARE PLACES SUCH AS ABANDONED
STRUCTURES,
FORTRESSES, SHRINES, OR CAVES.
WHAT THEY HAVE IN COMMON IS
THEY'RE ENCLOSED AREAS
WHERE IT'S EASY FOR MONSTERS
TO GET THE DROP ON YOU.
A LOT OF DUNGEONS ARE HOME
TO LOW‐LEVEL MONSTERS.
HOWEVER, WHAT SEEMS LIKE
A LACK OF MONSTERS
CAN MEAN SOMETHING HUGE,
LIKE A DRAGON IS GUARDING
A TREASURE THERE.
BIG DRAGON, ENCLOSED SPACE...
NOT GOOD FOR ADVENTURERS.
AND IT'S A WHOLE LOT HARDER
THAN FIGHTING ONE IN THE OPEN.
YOUR TEAMWORK HAS
TO BE IMPECCABLE
OR YOU WON'T LAST LONG.
(SLOW WALTZ)
[SHIROE] I KNOW THIS MUSIC.
HM.
[SHIROE, THINKING] IT'S KIND
OF STRANGE, BUT THIS IS THE
OPENING THEME TO "ELDER TALES."
[SERJIAD] ONCE YOUNG LADIES
IN EASTAL COME OF AGE,
THEY MAKE THEIR SOCIAL
DEBUT AT A FORMAL BALL.
THE 10‐DAY CONFERENCE
BEGINNING TOMORROW ALSO HOLDS
A SIMILAR PROMISE FOR
US TO GET ACQUAINTED.
(SLOW WALTZ CONTINUES)
[SERJIAD] SO WHY DON'T
YOU JOIN THE DANCE?
[SHIROE] EHH?
[MICHITAKA] HUH?
HA HA! TAKE A
LOOK OUT THERE.
THEY'RE ALL FASCINATED
WITH YOU. HOW ABOUT IT?
AH. WHAT ABOUT YOU, MISS?
YOUR GRACE, I AM
MY LORD'S NINJA.
I CANNOT BE SEEN DOING SOMETHING
LIKE THAT IN PUBLIC. AAH!
(SHIROE CHUCKLES WEAKLY)
THEN HOW ABOUT YOU?
[MICHITAKA] NO, NO.
I'M MORE OF A ROUGHNECK
THAN SOME DANCER GUY.
[SHIROE] YOU KNOW, I‐I THINK
THE OBVIOUS CHOICE IS‐
YOU. AM I RIGHT?
[SHIROE] UH!
[KRUSTY] SINCE I REPRESENT
THE ROUND TABLE,
I THINK IT'S APPROPRIATE
THAT I SHOULD TALK MORE
WITH HIS LORDSHIP.
[SHIROE, WHISPERING]
I'M GONNA KILL YOU.
(KRUSTY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
[SHIROE, THINKING] YOU'RE
ENJOYING THIS, AREN'T YOU?
MIGHT AS WELL EMBARRASS
MYSELF AND GET IT OVER WITH.
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE...
[SHIROE] HUH?
A GENTLEMAN MUST NEVER ALLOW
HIS LACK OF CONFIDENCE TO SHOW.
RIGHT NOW YOU'RE A MEMBER OF
THE ROUND TABLE'S DELEGATION.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
OK. SINCE YOU'RE BEING
SUCH A GOOD BOY,
I'LL SHARE A LITTLE
MAGIC GIFT WITH YOU.
(SHIROE GRUNTING)
[SHIROE] EH, HENRIETTA?
SHIROE, TRY TO SMILE.
AND STAND UP
STRAIGHT FOR ME, OK?
PUT YOUR HAND ON MY HIP.
YOU DO KNOW I CAN'T
DANCE, RIGHT?
THIS IS BOUND TO GET
REALLY EMBARRASSING.
YOU ARE AWARE OF WHAT MY
CLASS IS, AREN'T YOU, SHIROE?
WHAT YOUR CLASS IS?
[HENRIETTA] I AM A BARD.
JUST LET ME LEAD YOU.
NOW, THEN LET'S DANCE.
[SHIROE] UH, UH!
(ISUZU PLAYING
STRINGED INSTRUMENT)
(TOYA SNORING)
[RUNDELLHAUS] IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'RE A BARD, MISS ISUZU, YES?
[ISUZU] HMM? HEE HEE!
[RUNDELLHAUS] THAT WAS
ABSOLUTELY ELEGANT.
IT PERFECTLY SUITS
THIS CLEAR NIGHT AIR!
[ISUZU] YOU'RE
EXAGGERATING. HA HA!
[SERARA] UM, WHAT'S
A BARD, MASTER?
[NYANTA] ONE OF THE
WEAPON‐BASED OFFENSIVE CLASSES.
BUT UNLIKE THE ASSASSIN
OR SWASHBUCKLER,
THEY PLAY A SUPPORT ROLE
IN MOST PARTIES, HMM.
A SUPPORT ROLE?
ISN'T THAT KIND OF WHAT
AN ENCHANTER DOES?
[MINORI] HOLD ON.
"SPECIALIZES IN
LOWERING ENEMY STATS
OR ENHANCING THE ABILITIES
OF THEIR ALLIES,"
OR SO I'VE BEEN TOLD.
[NYANTA] YEAH. YOU CAN READ, BUT
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT MEANS?
(MINORI SIGHS)
[NAOTSUGU] THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN BARDS AND ENCHANTERS
IS THAT THEY USE MUSIC.
[NYANTA] ONE OTHER TRAIT THAT
DISTINGUISHES A BARD IS
THE LONG DURATION OF MANY
OF THEIR ABILITIES, HUH.
[HENRIETTA, VOICE‐CHAT]
ALL RIGHT. ARE YOU
GETTING THE HANG OF IT?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT]
I'M GETTING THERE.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
BASICALLY IT'S LIKE
ONE OF THOSE RHYTHM GAMES.
[HENRIETTA, VOICE‐CHAT]
RIGHT STEP, RIGHT FORWARD,
HALF‐TURN!
HA HA! THAT'S IT!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT]
THANKS, TEACHER.
[HENRIETTA] OH, MY.
[SHIROE] MUSIC... WOW. I'D
FORGOT HOW MATHEMATICAL IT WAS.
(SONG ENDS)
(CROWD MURMURING)
(YOUNGSTERS LAUGHING)
[BOY IN VEST] UH...
[AKATSUKI] DID YOU
HURT YOURSELF?
NO, NO. I'M FINE.
UH, WHERE YOU ARE FROM?
HUH?
AH, COME AND PLAY WITH US.
HANGING OUT WITH ALL THESE
GROWNUPS IS SO LAME.
WE'RE PLAYING
HIDE AND GO SEEK.
[GIRL] HURRY UP,
YOU GUYS!
[BOY IN VEST] SHE DISAPPEARED!
[BOY IN JACKET] WHOA!
[GIRL] WOW! SHE'S A GENIUS
AT HIDE‐AND‐SEEK!
(SHIROE YAWNS)
[SHIROE] I AM BEAT.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
UH, H‐HELLO?
[MINORI, VOICE‐CHAT]
SHIROE, YOU GOT TIME TO TALK?
[SHIROE] HEY, MINORI,
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
[MINORI] WELL, WE'RE HEADED
INTO THE DUNGEON IN THE
FOREST OF LAGLANDA TOMORROW.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT]
AND YOU'RE WORRIED.
(MINORI SIGHS)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT]
YOU MIGHT HAVE A ROUGH GO OF IT
SINCE YOU AND EVERYONE
YOU'RE TEAMING UP WITH IS
KIND OF LOW, LEVEL‐WISE.
[MINORI] I'M WORRIED I'M
GONNA SLOW EVERYONE DOWN.
NAOTSUGU AND THE OTHER
TRAINERS WON'T BE THERE.
JUST LISTEN, MINORI.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BE ALONE, OK?
ALSO, YOU DON'T WIN A BATTLE
WITH JUST YOUR LEVEL.
YOU REMEMBER THE BASICS OF
PARTY TACTICS, RIGHT?
UH, YEAH. GOT IT RIGHT HERE.
FORMATION, OPERATOR,
FIELD MONITOR,
AND PATROL TEAMS, RIGHT?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT]
THOSE ARE THE BASICS.
NOW YOU JUST HAVE
TO IMPLEMENT THEM.
I KNOW YOU CAN DO THIS.
[MINORI] YEAH.
I SHOULD HAVE LEARNED
THIS ALREADY.
UNFORTUNATELY, THERE'S NO BETTER
TEACHER THAN EXPERIENCE.
GO GET 'EM.
[KAYU] OH, GOD! THIS IS SO GOOD!
I'M FREAKING OUT OVER HERE!
[MICHITAKA] LOOKS LIKE
THE NOBILITY GETS ALONG
PRETTY WELL AT BREAKFAST.
[SHIROE] IT WOULD SEEM THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND BROUGHT
OUR COOKING SECRET
BACK HERE WITH THEM.
IF I GET WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT,
THEN WE'RE AFFECTING
THIS WORLD. I MEAN DIRECTLY.
YOU ARE. AND NOW WE NEED
TO MAKE SURE OUR NEXT
STEPS AREN'T DESTRUCTIVE.
SO WE NEED TO LEARN
WHAT WE CAN AND TREAD
LIGHTLY WHILE DOING IT.
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
I THINK I'VE STARTED TO
GET A GRASP ON WHAT YOU'VE
BEEN TALKING ABOUT.
BY THE WAY, SHIROE, I'M ASSUMING
YOU SLEPT WELL LAST NIGHT.
[MICHITAKA] BET YOU HAD
A HELL OF A WORKOUT, HUH?
[KRUSTY] LET'S NOT TIP
ANY GLASSES, MICHITAKA.
[SHIROE] I SLEPT
JUST FINE, THANKS.
KRUSTY, ONE OF THESE DAYS
YOU'RE GONNA GET IT.
[AKATSUKI] I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE THE TYPE TO HOLD A GRUDGE
AGAINST SOMEONE, MY LORD.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ABOVE ALL THAT.
OH? YOU SEEM GROUCHY.
MAYBE YOU DIDN'T
GET ENOUGH SLEEP.
YOU'RE IMAGINING THINGS.
[SHIROE] GROUCHY.
[AKATSUKI] NO, I'M NOT.
[SHIROE] YES, YOU ARE.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD...
[SHIROE] WHAT?
[AKATSUKI] JAM.
[SHIROE] UH...
[AKATSUKI] PASS ME THE JAM.
[SHIROE] OH, YEAH. SURE THING.
(KAYU SLURPS)
[SHIROE] BY THE WAY,
MICHITAKA,
YOU'D KNOW THIS BETTER
THAN I WOULD, BUT DID
WE BRING ANY CHEFS?
HMM, WE
BROUGHT A FEW.
WE MIGHT NEED TO CALL FOR
MORE PEOPLE FROM THE CITY.
DEFINITELY.
WHAT DO WE
NEED THEM FOR?
JUST TAKE A LOOK AT
THE SIZE OF THIS TERRACE.
THEY ARE EXPECTING A
LOT MORE COMPANY.
HMM? WHAT COMPANY?
WAIT. NOBLEMEN?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE CONFERENCE LASTS
FOR 10 DAYS.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE THERE'S
WALL‐TO‐WALL EVENTS
GOING ON EVERY DAY.
THE MAJORITY IS BACKROOM
DEALS AND PRIVATE MEETINGS,
LIKE A BUNCH OF
LITTLE TEA PARTIES.
THE POLITICS HERE
ARE A LITTLE TOUGH
FOR ME TO GET MY HEAD AROUND.
HOWEVER, I HEARD THAT
THERE'S 24 NOBLE HOUSES
IN EASTAL'S LEAGUE
OF FREEDOM CITIES.
ADD THE ROUND TABLE,
AND THAT'S 25.
LORD SERJIAD'S CITY OF
MAIHAMA HAS A POPULATION
OF 30,000 OR SO.
[TAKAYAMA] SO IN
TERMS OF PURE NUMBERS,
A CITY LIKE AKIHABARA
IS KIND OF SMALL WHEN YOU
CONSIDER WE ONLY HAVE 20,000.
[SHIROE] I ALREADY HAVE AN
IDEA OF WHAT THE NOBLES
WANT TO FIND OUT.
FIRST AND FOREMOST,
FIND OUT WHAT AMBITIONS
THE ADVENTURERS HAVE
AND THE POLITICAL ASPIRATIONS
OF THE ROUND TABLE.
BUT LAST NIGHT AT THE BALL,
IT'S LIKELY THAT WE DISPELLED
SOME OF THOSE CONCERNS.
[KRUSTY] OK, THEN. SO THEIR NEXT
PLAY IS GOING TO BE GETTING US
TO WORK FOR THEM.
[SHIROE] RIGHT. REMEMBER,
SINCE THE APOCALYPSE,
WE HAVEN'T RECEIVED A
SINGLE QUEST FROM THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
(CLOCK GONGS)
[KILIVA] THE MAY INCIDENT
IS CERTAINLY THE CAUSE
OF ALL THIS TROUBLE.
THE ADVENTURERS SUPPOSEDLY REFER
TO IT AS "THE APOCALYPSE."
UNTIL NOW, THE ADVENTURERS OF
AKIHABARA WERE PRETTY FRAGMENTED
AND DISORGANIZED.
WHICH, OF COURSE,
MADE THOSE INGRATES MUCH
MORE EASY TO DEAL WITH.
[DALTE] THEY WERE
ALWAYS QUITE USEFUL
IN EXTERMINATING MONSTERS
AND GUARDING CARAVANS.
AS LONG AS YOU PAID THEM,
THEY WERE PRETTY MUCH
WILLING TO DO ANYTHING.
BUT EVER SINCE THIS
APOCALYPSE OF THEIRS,
THEY HAVE HARDLY VENTURED
OUTSIDE OF THEIR CITY
TO HELP US AT ALL.
(CLOCK GONGS)
AND NOW THEY'VE FOUNDED
THAT ROUND TABLE.
I GUESS THEY'RE MAKING
AN ATTEMPT TO RULE THEIR
CITY JUST LIKE WE DO.
(CLOCK GONGS)
I'VE HEARD THEY'RE
DEVELOPING NEW TECHNOLOGY
AT A RAPID PACE.
WE HAVE TO GET THEIR BRIGHTEST
MINDS WORKING FOR US QUICKLY.
OTHERWISE, WE'RE GOING TO
WIND UP HAVING THE WHOLE LOT
OF THEM LEAVE US BEHIND!
[SHIROE] WHAT THEY'LL NEED IS
OUR POWER AND ABILITIES.
BUT THEY'LL NEVER ACT LIKE
WE'RE SUPERIOR TO THEM AT ALL.
THERE'S A POSSIBILITY THEY MIGHT
GRANT A NOBLE TITLE TO KRUSTY
OR TO THE ROUND
TABLE AS AN ENTITY.
THEY'RE ALWAYS GONNA TRY
TO MAKE US BEHOLDEN TO THEM.
THE PROBLEM IS HOW
TO DEAL WITH THEM
WHEN THEY COME TO
US INDIVIDUALLY
RATHER THAN THROUGH
THE ROUND TABLE.
THAT'LL BE KIND
OF TOUGH.
[SHIROE] CHANCES ARE GOOD THAT
IT'S GONNA BE LIKE THE GAME
WHERE NOBLES GO TO THE
GUILDS OR INDIVIDUALS
TO DO THEIR BIDDING.
I'M SURE THE WARRIOR AND
CRAFTING GUILDS WILL WANT
WHATEVER THE NOBLES OFFER THEM,
JUST LIKE THE GAME.
NO DOUBT IN MY MIND.
[MICHITAKA] POWERFUL INDIVIDUALS
WON'T SAY NO EITHER.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR
THE ROUND TABLE
TO MONITOR EVERYONE
ALL THE TIME,
NOR IS IT OUR PURPOSE
TO BEGIN WITH.
MAYBE, BUT WE PROBABLY
STILL NEED TO LAY DOWN
SOME GUIDELINES.
[SHIROE] AND THAT'S ONE
REASON IT'S SO IMPORTANT
FOR US TO KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE THINKING.
SO IT'S YOUR TURN,
AKATSUKI. YOU'RE UP.
[AKATSUKI] HUH?
[SHIROE]
RECONNAISSANCE, PLEASE.
[AKATSUKI] HM. I'M ON MY WAY.
(GRUNTING)
[RUNDELLHAUS] HUH?
[NYANTA] WELCOME TO THE
FOREST OF LAGLANDA.
[NYANTA] IT'S RATHER
EXPANSIVE INSIDE,
BUT BASICALLY AT THE
FIRST FORK IN THE PATH,
THE RIGHT SIDE LEADS
TO THE BEGINNER COURSE.
THE LEFT IS FOR
INTERMEDIATE PLAYERS.
HMM.
DON'T PUSH YOURSELVES TOO HARD.
TRAINING INVOLVES KNOWING
YOUR CURRENT LIMITS
AND WORKING WITH THEM, HMM?
[NAOTSUGU] THAT'S RIGHT.
DON'T GET YOURSELVES KILLED.
[REZARICK] LISTEN UP, GUYS.
YOU'LL ALL BE CAMPING
IN THE CLEARING HERE
AND GOING INTO THE
DUNGEON EVERY DAY.
I'LL BE HERE TO GIVE YOU FURTHER
TRAINING AFTER YOU GET OUT.
(CLAPS HANDS)
ALL RIGHT! LET'S SPLIT UP
INTO OUR COMBAT TEAMS, PEOPLE.
PICK WHO YOU WANT
TO ADVENTURE WITH
AND HOLD YOUR STRATEGY MEETINGS.
THEN HIT THE DUNGEON!
[YOUNG PLAYERS] YES, SIR!
[TOYA] OK, EVERYBODY,
WHY DON'T WE START
BY INTRODUCING OURSELVES?
I'M TOYA. I'M A SAMURAI,
AND I'M LEVEL 29.
LET ME HANDLE
THE FRONT LINES, OK?
I'M SERARA.
I'M A DRUID AND A HEALER.
AND I'M AT LEVEL 25.
I'M NOT GOOD AT ATTACKING STUFF,
BUT LEAVE THE HEALING TO ME!
I'M ISUZU,
AND I'M A BARD CLASS.
I'LL BE HELPING WHEN IT'S
TIME TO ATTACK SOMETHING.
I'M AT LEVEL 24.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M MINORI.
I AM A SHRINE MAIDEN.
AND MY SPECIALTY IS
CASTING DEFENSIVE MAGIC.
I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO WORKING WITH SERARA
TO KEEP ALL OF YOU HEALTHY
AND OUT OF THE CATHEDRAL.
I'M AT LEVEL...
(MOANS SOFTLY)
...AT LEVEL 21.
YOU'RE LEVEL 21? HMPH!
DO ME A FAVOR AND
DON'T SLOW ME DOWN.
HMPH. WHO ARE YOU?
MM‐HMM. I AM NONE OTHER THAN
THE MIGHTY RUNDELLHAUS CODE.
BUT IF YOU FIND
YOURSELF IN A HURRY,
YOU CAN ALWAYS CALL ME RUDY.
[TOYA] WHAT'S
YOUR CLASS?
[RUDY] ISN'T MY APPAREL
AND APPEARANCE
THE DEAD GIVEAWAY?
I'M A SORCERER, OF COURSE.
YOU SURE TALK A LOT, DON'T YOU?
WHAT'S YOUR LEVEL?
(RUDY CHUCKLES)
23, MY FRIENDS.
[TOYA] SO WHY ARE YOU GIVING
MY SISTER A HARD TIME?!
THERE'S NO NEED TO FEAR.
MY GRACEFUL YET
DEVASTATING TECHNIQUE
WILL ANNIHILATE
OUR ENEMY.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS STAND
BACK AND SUPPORT ME, OK?
[TOYA] SORCERERS DON'T
FIGHT UP FRONT, STUPID!
[RUDY] TRY NOT TO GET
CAUGHT UP IN THE SEMANTICS.
HA HA!
[SERARA] UM, HEY.
SO IF IT'S OK,
WHY DON'T WE WORK ON
OUR STRATEGY?
[TOYA] WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO BE DOING ANYWAY?
[ISUZU] YEAH. I REALLY
DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA.
[MINORI] HEY, GUYS, I KNOW.
MAYBE WE SHOULD START
WITH OUR BASIC FORMATION
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT‐
[RUDY]
THERE'S NOTHING TO IT!
WE JUST NEED TO GET FIRED UP
AND READY FOR COMBAT!
I DON'T KNOW...
[TOYA] OH, YEAH!
THAT'S RIGHT, BABY!
I'M ABOUT TO KICK
SOME MONSTER BUTT!
[MINORI] MAYBE NOT.
LET'S TAKE THAT DUNGEON!
THAT'S RIGHT! WHO'S THE MAN?!
YES, BUT ALSO REMEMBER TO
BE ELEGANT IN ALL THINGS.
BUT A MAN MUST BE CRANKED UP
AND RAGING TO WIN THE DAY!
COME ON, NOW!
LET'S DO THIS! WHOO!
(BOYS LAUGHING)
(TOYA LAUGHS)
[RUDY] YEAH!
[MINORI, THINKING]
WHY ARE BOYS SUCH BOYS?
RIGHT. LET'S GO.
(SERARA WHIMPERS)
[NAOTSUGU] TOYA, DO YOU REMEMBER
WHAT YOU PROMISED ME?
[TOYA] SENSEI?
[NAOTSUGU] THE JOB OF
A FRONT‐LINE TANK IS
TO ABSORB ALL THE ENEMY HITS
AND TO ALWAYS TRUST THE
REST OF HIS GROUP.
TOYA, AS A MAN, YOU MUST
PROMISE TO BE AWESOME.
I REMEMBER, SENSEI.
RIGHT ON, LITTLE MAN.
[NYANTA] HMM?
LITTLE MINORI,
WHAT'S WRONG, HMM?
OH, I, UH, IT'S NOTHING, REALLY.
LISTEN, IF YOU EVER
HAVE A PROBLEM,
YOU MUST STEP FORWARD.
BUT NOT WITH YOUR LEGS;
WITH YOUR HEART.
WITH MY HEART? RIGHT!
(SERARA WHIMPERING)
(SERARA SCREAMING)
(ISUZU SCREAMING)
[TOYA] WHAT'S GOING ON?
[RUDY] MONSTERS NOW?
[MINORI] CALM DOWN, DANG IT!
WE NEED SOME LIGHT FIRST!
[RUDY] YOUR WISH
IS MY COMMAND.
[ISUZU] I HOPE THE ENEMY
DOESN'T USE THAT AS A BEACON.
[RUDY] WELL, I'M HOPING
THEY'LL DO EXACTLY THAT!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
[MINORI] MOST OF THE ENEMIES
HERE ARE OF THE UNDEAD VARIETY.
[SERARA] THAT'S RIGHT.
THE UNDEAD CAN SEE
US IN THE DARK.
SO IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF WE HAVE LIGHT.
BUT WE'RE NOT BETTER OFF
FUMBLING AROUND WITHOUT IT.
IGNITING FOX LIGHT!
[RUDY] GRR! MINE IS
BRIGHTER, SEE?!
LOOK AT THAT!
[SERARA] THIS ISN'T A
COMPETITION, YOU SHOWOFF!
WHAT HAPPENS IF YOUR
LIGHT GOES OUT, HUH?!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
HAVE MORE THAN ONE!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SAYING
MY LIGHT WAS WEAK OR
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE
'CAUSE I'M AWESOME! HA HA!
(GROANS)
[ISUZU] UH, NOT GOOD.
[MINORI] IT LOOKS LIKE ONE OF
THE GROUPS THAT WENT BEFORE US
BATTLED A FEW SKELETONS HERE.
[RUDY] HMM?
[SERARA] THERE'S A
FORK UP AHEAD.
[ISUZU] UM, WASN'T THE
RIGHT FOR BEGINNERS
AND THE LEFT FOR
INTERMEDIATE PLAYERS?
[TOYA] LOOKS LIKE THE GROUP
AHEAD OF US WENT LEFT.
LET'S GO THIS WAY. COME ON.
[RUDY] YEAH, SURE.
JUST DON'T THINK I'M GONNA TAKE
THE EASY PATH EVERY TIME, OK?
HOLD UP. HEY, RUNDELLHAUS?
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE TO CAST
YOUR MAGIC FROM THE BACK.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, MISS MINORI?
THE BATTLE BEGINS THE MOMENT
THE ENEMY IS IN SIGHT.
I DON'T HAVE THE TIME TO WASTE
WAITING ON EVERYONE ELSE
WHILE I CAN CAST MY SPELLS
FROM THE FRONT OF OUR FORMATION.
(MINORI SIGHS)
[MINORI, THINKING]
I GUESS I'LL JUST HELP HIM
IF HE GETS INTO TROUBLE.
I CAN'T HEAL AS WELL AS SERARA,
EVEN THOUGH WE'RE BOTH HEALERS.
BUT MY MAGIC CAN CANCEL A
CERTAIN AMOUNT OF ENEMY DAMAGE.
(BELLS JINGLE)
THE SAMURAI'S STRENGTH IS
ITS POWERFUL ATTACKS,
BUT THEY HAVE A LONG
COOL DOWN PERIOD.
TIMING THEIR ATTACK IS
THE TRICKY PART.
[TOYA] UH!
[TOYA] WAIT UP.
[ALL] HM?
WE'VE GOT 3.
ALL RIGHT.
WATCH AND LEARN.
(CRACK)
(RUDY YELPS)
[MINORI] TOYA! DON'T JUST
CHARGE STRAIGHT IN THERE!
[TOYA] I KNOW!
IIZUNA SLASH!
SAMURAI CAN ALSO ATTACK
AT LONG DISTANCES.
NOW COME GET SOME!
OK!
HE WAS DRAWING THE
SKELETONS' ATTENTION.
[TOYA] WHIRLWIND SLASH!
(RUDY CHUCKLES)
HOW YOU LIKE THAT?!
(SWORD RATTLES)
[TOYA] UGH!
UH! PURIFICATION BARRIER!
OH, NO. I NEED TO USE MY
MAGIC FIRST OR IT WON'T WORK!
(TOYA GRUNTS)
HEARTBEAT HEALING!
[MINORI] TOYA, YOU'VE GOT
10 SECONDS UNTIL YOU'RE
ALL HEALED UP!
NOT TOO SHABBY, MR. TOYA.
BUT YOU HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYTHING YET!
ORB OF LAVA!
AMAZING!
IT HAS LIMITED RANGE,
BUT IT'S POWERFUL!
[SERARA] IS THIS THE TRUE
POWER OF THE SORCERER,
THE MAGICAL ATTACK CLASS?
(MUSICAL NOTES)
HUH? HUH?! WHOA!
HUH? WHAT?
[ISUZU] AWESOME!
IT TOTALLY WORKED!
[MINORI] ISUZU, WHAT
DID YOU DO JUST NOW?
I SET UP A SUPPORT SONG
BEFORE THE BATTLE STARTED.
THE REPEATING CAROL...
IF A PARTY MEMBER
ATTACKS WITH MAGIC,
IT AUTOMATICALLY LAUNCHES
ANOTHER ATTACK.
AMAZINGLY ADEQUATE,
MISS ISUZU.
MY ARTFULLY DESTRUCTIVE SPELLS
HAVE REACHED THE LEVEL OF
THE MOST LEGENDARY SORCERERS
THAT EVER CAST A SPELL!
NICELY PLAYED! GRAZIE.
HA HA HA!
HUH?
(MINORI GASPS)
RUNDELLHAUS, BEHIND YOU!
HUH? WHAT'S THE MATTER,
MISS MINORI?
HAVE YOU FALLEN IN LOVE
WITH MY MAGICAL MAGIC?
[MINORI] NO! THEY'RE
AIMING AT YOU.
[RUDY] PRESTO.
HUH?
AAH! WHAT'S GOING ON?!
THEY'VE GOT ARCHERS?
[MINORI] WAIT, TOYA!
WE HAVEN'T CLEARED THAT
PART OF THE CAVE YET!
[TOYA] HUH?
[TOYA] GREAT. THERE'S 5 OF THEM.
TOYA, GET BACK HERE!
NO, I'VE GOT ALL MY HEALTH BACK!
I'LL TAKE 'EM!
(SERARA WHIMPERS)
[MINORI, THINKING] THEY'RE
GONNA ATTACK HIM ON ALL SIDES.
I MUST REMAIN CALM.
FIRST I SHOULD CAST MAGIC
TO PROTECT THE FRONT ROW!
HUH?
NO, IT'S TAKING TOO
LONG TO CAST!
THEN I'LL JUST BURN
THIS BUNCH OF BONES
TO ASH AGAIN.
[TOYA] WAIT UP! HUH?
[RUDY] HEY!
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?!
NOW, HOW CAN HIS AGGRO RATING
BE HIGHER THAN TOYA'S IS?
(SLASHING)
[RUDY] UGH! AH!
[RUDY] NOT COOL, MAN! AAH!
[SERARA] IT'S NO GOOD!
I CAN'T HEAL YOU IN TIME
AT THAT RATE, RUNDELL!
ONLY ONE THING LEFT TO DO.
[TOYA] RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!
[RUDY] HUH?
[RUDY] THIS IS SO LAME!
I MEAN, THIS IS SO NOT AWESOME!
[RAYNESHIA] (SIGH)
[KILIVA] I MUST SAY, YOUR
ARMY'S EXTREMELY FORTUNATE
TO HAVE A COMMANDER
LIKE YOU AT THE HELM.
YOUR STRENGTH IS AMAZING.
IT RIVALS THAT OF
THE EASTERN KNIGHTS.
[KRUSTY] THAT'S AWFULLY
FLATTERING OF YOU.
[KILIVA] SO HOW ABOUT IT?
I BROUGHT SOME FINE
SPIRITS FROM MY HOMELAND.
THE SUN'S SETTING. WHY DON'T
YOU JOIN ME FOR A DRINK?
[KRUSTY] HUH?
AH. HM.
HMM...
[KRUSTY] I'M SORRY, LORD KILIVA,
BUT I ACTUALLY HAVE OTHER
PLANS FOR TONIGHT.
[KILIVA] HUH? YOU HAVE
ANOTHER ENGAGEMENT?
OH, PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
I UNDERSTAND.
WELL, THERE'S NO WAY
I'D INTERFERE WITH THAT.
[KRUSTY] PLEASED TO
MEET YOU, MILADY.
I'M THE ADVENTURER
THEY CALL KRUSTY.
UH...
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
THE WINTER ROSE OF EASTAL.
LONG, SILVERY HAIR, A DELICATE
CURVE TO HER NECK,
AND A MYSTERIOUS LIGHT IN
HER BLUE‐GRAY EYES.
HER NAME IS
RAYNESHIA EL‐ARTE COWEN.
AND SHE DREAMS OF LYING IN A
BED ALL DAY IN HER PAJAMAS.
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.