[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] IN ALL
THIS TIME, MINORI HAS NEVER
REALLY ASKED FOR MY HELP.
ADVICE, YES.
STRATEGY AND KNOWLEDGE, YES.
BUT UNTIL NOW, SHE'S
NEVER COME RIGHT OUT
AND ASKED FOR HELP.
SO SOMETHING'S WRONG.
[MINORI] PLEASE HELP US!
WE HAVE A CASUALTY!
IT'S RUNDELLHAUS.
A DIRE WOLF GOT HIM.
THERE'S SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
HE'S ONE OF THE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
GET A HOLD OF KARASHIN.
HE'S GOING TO BE TAKING OVER.
[NEMIMI] HUH?
(GRIFFIN WHISTLE)
[SHIROE, THINKING] THERE ARE
SOME THINGS I CAN'T DO,
NOT EVEN HERE IN
THIS TWISTED WORLD,
THIS WORLD WITHOUT
MANY LIMITATIONS. BUT...
MINORI CALLED.
AND I'M GONNA TRY.
(GRIFFIN SCREECHING)
[SHIROE] WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
[MINORI, VOICE‐CHAT]
RUNDELLHAUS WAS FATALLY WOUNDED
WHILE DEFENDING CHOSHI.
WE'VE CAST TWO REVIVAL SPELLS,
BUT THEY HAVEN'T WORKED.
HE STILL HAS A PULSE, AND HE'S
STILL WARM TO THE TOUCH.
BUT HE HASN'T COME AROUND YET.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
[SHIROE] WHERE ARE YOU EXACTLY
AND WHO'S THERE WITH YOU?
[MINORI] IT'S TOYA, ISUZU,
SERARA, AND ME...
AND RUNDELLHAUS.
AND, LET'S SEE, WE'RE
NEAR THE CROSSROADS.
IT'S PRETTY CLOSE TO
THE CENTER OF TOWN.
[SHIROE] IS IT SAFE?
[MINORI] THERE AREN'T
ANY GOBLINS HERE,
BUT THERE'S STILL A LOT OF
FIGHTING GOING ON AT THE COAST.
I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
COMING BACK TO THIS
PART OF TOWN OR NOT.
[TOYA] SHIROE, WE NEED
YOU TO HELP SAVE RUDY!
I'M THE ONE WHO BROUGHT RUDY
HERE IN THE FIRST PLACE.
IT'S MY FAULT.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
(CRYING)
WE REALLY DO NEED YOUR
HELP DOWN HERE. PLEASE!
[SHIROE] HAVE SERARA CAST
A REVIVAL SPELL.
[MINORI] RIGHT.
[SHIROE] WAIT 150 SECONDS.
HAVE TOYA KEEP WATCH.
ISUZU SHOULD USE A MAGIC
POINT RESTORATION SONG.
AFTER THAT 150 SECONDS,
CAST ANOTHER REVIVAL SPELL.
[MINORI] OK!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE ENERGY THAT ANIMATES
HUMANS AND DEMI‐HUMANS
IS CALLED THE SPIRIT.
IT HAS 2 PARTS.
PSYCHE IS THE ENERGY
THAT ANIMATES THE MIND.
THIS IS THE SOURCE OF MAGIC.
AND IT'S EXPRESSED
AS MAGIC POINTS.
[REGAN] ANIMA IS THE ENERGY
THAT ANIMATES THE BODY.
YOU CALL THEM HIT
POINTS, OR HEALTH.
IT IS ALSO KNOWN AS KI OR CHI.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] WHEN
SOMEONE IS DEFEATED IN BATTLE,
THEY CAN NO LONGER MOVE.
BUT THE MIND REMAINS HEALTHY.
THEN THE ANIMA DISPERSAL BEGINS.
ANIMA DISPERSAL IS
WHEN THE ANIMA, THE BODY,
IS DISPERSED AND VANISHES.
REVIVAL MAGIC GATHERS
THE ANIMA DISPERSED
INTO THE SURROUNDING ATMOSPHERE
AND PUTS IT BACK TOGETHER.
REGAN HAD A HYPOTHESIS THAT
YOU COULD USE THE REVIVAL MAGIC
ON AN NPC IF YOU USED IT
IMMEDIATELY AFTER SOMEONE DIED.
IF HE STILL HAS A PULSE,
THEN HIS BODY AND HIS ANIMA
COULD BE SUCCESSFULLY RESTORED.
BUT IF HE'S STILL UNCONSCIOUS,
THEN HIS PSYCHE,
THE POWER OF HIS MIND
HAS STARTED TO DISSIPATE.
AND THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
IN DANGER OF LOSING.
THE MIND DISPERSES
ALONG WITH THE BODY,
EACH BECOMING UNENTANGLED.
AND WHEN THE BODY IS
COMPLETELY GONE,
THE MIND HAS NOWHERE TO RETURN,
MAKING REVIVAL IMPOSSIBLE.
THIS IS THE POINT AT WHICH
PEOPLE OF THE LAND DIE.
ADVENTURERS, ON THE OTHER HAND,
FIND THEMSELVES REINCARNATED
AT THE CATHEDRAL.
PSYCHE AND ANIMA ARE REJOINED,
AND LIFE CONTINUES.
[MINORI] WE ARE AT 150 SECONDS.
STARTING MY NEXT REVIVAL SPELL.
[SHIROE] IN ANOTHER 150,
USE THE REVIVAL SPELL AGAIN.
I'M STARTING MY DESCENT.
KEEP ON ALTERNATING YOUR
SPELLS FOR ANOTHER 8 MINUTES.
[MINORI] OK!
[SHIROE, THINKING] ALL WE CAN DO
RIGHT NOW IS MAKE SURE HIS BODY
DOESN'T BREAK UP ANY MORE.
BUT THEN WHAT?
[KANAMI] NOW, SHIROE,
ISN'T IT YOUR JOB
TO THINK OF SOLUTIONS?
[SHIROE] UH, BUT, YEAH. MAYBE.
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN I CAN
JUST WHISK YOU AWAY TO SEE
THE MIDNIGHT SUN IN ICELAND.
[KANAMI] OH, COME ON. BUT I
REALLY WANT TO SEE IT, SHIROE.
I'M A DREAMER, YOU KNOW.
AND YOU MAKE MY DREAMS
COME TRUE, RIGHT?
[SHIROE] YEAH, I GET IT.
[AKATSUKI] UH?
[REGAN] MY OWN SPECIALTY IS
A LITTLE SOMETHING THAT I LIKE
TO REFER TO AS WORLD‐CLASS
MAGIC AND ENCHANTMENTS.
[SHIROE] AH! MAGIC THAT
ALTERS THE RULES THAT
MAKE THE WORLD WORK.
OH! AKATSUKI, REINS.
THERE YOU ARE.
(STREAM FLOWING)
(SPLASH)
[TAKAYAMA] MILORD...
I'VE BROUGHT THE REPORT.
[KRUSTY] THANK YOU.
[RAYNESHIA] UH...
SO AWKWARD.
[KRUSTY] HOW ARE WE
DOING OUT THERE?
WELL, PRINCESS, YOU'RE GETTING
RATHER POPULAR, AREN'T YOU?
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[MAN 1] SHE LOOKED AT ME!
[MAN 2] WHOA. NORTHERN
GIRLS ARE GORGEOUS...
[MAN 3] SOMEBODY TAKE A PICTURE!
(RAYNESHIA CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(HOWLING IN DISTANCE)
(RAYNESHIA GASPS)
THOSE ARE
DIRE WOLVES.
PROBABLY THE
LARGER VARIETY.
[RAYNESHIA] IS IT
THE GOBLIN KING?
[KRUSTY] YOU WON'T CATCH HIM
OUTSIDE OF SEVENTH FALL.
MOST LIKELY, IT'S THE
GOBLIN GENERAL'S FORCES.
[RAYNESHIA] ALL RIGHT.
(WOLVES HOWLING)
(RAYNESHIA GASPS)
[KRUSTY] CLEANING UP
THEIR NEST CAN WAIT.
WE NEED TO PRESS
ON TO ZANTLEAF
AND DESTROY EVERY LAST ONE
OF THEM WHILE WE'RE THERE.
[SHIROE, THINKING] I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN REALLY DO IT
OR WHAT'LL HAPPEN IF IT WORKS.
THAT'LL DO.
THANKS, AKATSUKI.
(CHIME)
[SHIROE] AH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
[MINORI, VOICE‐CHAT] THE OCYPETE
HAS GOTTEN INTO CHOSHI.
BUT THE SAHUAGIN ARE TRYING
TO PREVENT THE LANDING.
I CAN HEAR THE
FIGHTING FROM HERE.
[MARIELLE] EVERYONE,
REINFORCEMENTS ARE HERE!
JUST A BIT MORE. JUST, LIKE,
HANG ON A BIT MORE!
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI, I NEED
YOU TO STAND WATCH.
[AKATSUKI] ROGER.
[SHIROE] GET EVERYONE
OUT OF THE AREA.
DON'T LET ANYONE NEAR,
PLAYERS OR MONSTERS.
[AKATSUKI] LEAVE IT TO ME.
[MINORI] SHIROE!
[TOYA] HE MADE IT!
[SHIROE] RUNDELLHAUS?
[MINORI] YES.
WE DID EVERYTHING YOU SAID.
YOUR PARTY...
ADD ME TO IT.
[MINORI] OK.
[SHIROE] YOU'RE ISUZU, RIGHT?
[ISUZU] HM?
[SHIROE] KEEP ON CASTING
MEDITATION NOCTURNE.
[ISUZU] RIGHT. OK.
[SHIROE] I'M GOING TO CAST
A NEW MAGIC SPELL.
[MINORI AND ISUZU] HM?
[SHIROE] TELL NO ONE ABOUT THIS.
[MINORI] A NEW SPELL?
YOU WILL AGREE
OR I WON'T DO IT.
AND THEN IT'S OVER.
[GROUP] MM‐HMM.
GOOD. LET'S BEGIN.
MANA‐CHANNELING.
[SERARA] I'VE NEVER
HEARD OF THAT BEFORE.
[MINORI] IT MEANS HE
CAN TAKE THE MAGIC POINTS
FROM ALL THE
MEMBERS OF A PARTY
AND GIVE IT BACK TO
EVERYONE EQUALLY.
BUT WHAT... WHAT FOR?
(CHILDREN SHUDDERING)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] PSYCHE
IS THE VESSEL OF THE MIND,
AND IT IS ALSO A
PERSON'S MAGIC POINTS.
AND THAT MEANS...
(GRUNTS)
[SHIROE] CAST ANOTHER
REVIVAL SPELL, MINORI.
SERARA, CONTINUOUS HEALING.
[MINORI] RIGHT!
[SERARA] RIGHT!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
RUNDELLHAUS NOW HAS MAGIC
POINTS TO POWER HIS MIND,
BUT HE'S STILL UNCONSCIOUS.
SO THE LINK BETWEEN
ANIMA AND PSYCHE,
HIS BODY AND MIND, IS STILL CUT.
WE'RE RACING AGAINST
TIME, EVERYONE.
REVIVAL INCENSE.
THIS WILL BRING HIM
BACK TO LIFE,
BUT HE'LL BE AS A ZOMBIE
AND ONLY FOR 3 MINUTES.
(GROUP GASPS)
WE CAN FORCE HIS MIND
AND BODY BACK TOGETHER,
BUT IT WON'T LAST LONG.
[SERARA] RUDY!
[MINORI] RUNDELLHAUS!
[TOYA] I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
HEY, RUDY! RUDY!
UH...
HMM? ISUZU?
HEY. WHERE AM I?
(WHIMPERING)
OH, I SEE. I DIED. I GUESS
I DIDN'T MAKE IT, HUH?
[RUDY] COME ON, GUYS.
IT ISN'T ALL THAT BAD.
IT'S JUST ONE OF THOSE THINGS
THAT HAPPENS TO
WARRIORS IN BATTLE.
IT'S NATURAL, RIGHT?
NATURAL, YOU SAY?
[RUDY] IT'S REALLY OK.
ALL I EVER WANTED TO DO WAS
BECOME AN ADVENTURER.
PLEASE DON'T BLAME MISS ISUZU
FOR KEEPING IT SECRET FROM YOU.
I ASKED HER TO
KEEP IT TO HERSELF,
AND SHE DID IT FOR ME.
[MINORI] I'M SORRY!
I KNEW ABOUT IT, RUDY.
I KNEW ABOUT IT!
I KNEW! BUT I...
[TOYA] MINORI...
HM. THANK YOU,
MISS MINORI.
DON'T LET IT BOTHER YOU.
[SHIROE] NO, BUT IT
DOES BOTHER ME.
LISTEN, RUNDELLHAUS CODE,
I COULD NEVER ALLOW SOMEONE
WHO GIVES UP SO EASILY CALL
HIMSELF AN ADVENTURER.
YOU GOT TO GIVE IT A
LOT MORE THAN THAT.
[MINORI] HUH?
[SHIROE] WHAT IN THE HELL
HAVE YOU LEARNED ANYWAY?
YOU DIDN'T JUST GO TO
THAT DUNGEON TO LEARN
STRATEGY AND TACTICS.
YOU WENT THERE TO
DEVELOP A WILL TO FIGHT,
A WILL TO WIN,
AND A WILL TO LIVE.
OR AM I WRONG ABOUT THAT?
[TOYA] BROTHER SHIROE...
RIGHT NOW, YOU ARE NOT AN
ADVENTURER. NOT EVEN CLOSE.
SO WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO
TO PROVE IT? TELL ME!
LISTEN TO ME,
AND LISTEN GOOD.
[SERARA] WHAT'S THAT?
[MINORI] IT'S A CONTRACT.
[SHIROE] A CONTRACT.
"I, SHIROE, LEADER OF
THE GUILD LOG HORIZON,
ESTABLISH THE FOLLOWING
CONTRACT WITH RUNDELLHAUS CODE.
ORDERS: ITEM 1. ON THE DATE
AND TIME RUNDELLHAUS CODE
EXECUTES THIS AGREEMENT, HE IS
ACCEPTED INTO LOG HORIZON.
HE BECOMES A FULL MEMBER
WITH ALL RIGHTS AND PRIVILEGES.
ITEM 2. AS A MEMBER OF
THE GUILD LOG HORIZON,
RUNDELLHAUS CODE WILL
FULFILL HIS MISSIONS
IN A MANNER BEFITTING
HIS POSITION
AND EXECUTE ALL MISSIONS
REQUIRED OF SAME.
ITEM 3. LOG HORIZON WILL
PROVIDE RUNDELLHAUS CODE ALL
LOGISTICAL SUPPORT NECESSARY
TO EXECUTE THE MISSIONS
TO WHICH HE IS ASSIGNED.
WHICH MEANS...
YOU ARE GRANTED THE STATUS
AND TITLE OF ADVENTURER."
(MINORI GASPS)
[SHIROE] "ITEM 4. THIS CONTRACT
WILL BE EXECUTED IN THE SPIRIT
MUTUAL RESPECT AND AGREEMENT
BETWEEN BOTH SIDES.
ANYTHING ACQUIRED
BY EITHER PARTY
FOR THE DURATION OF
THIS EXECUTED CONTRACT
REMAINS THEIRS,
EVEN IN THE EVENT THAT THE
CONTRACT IS NULLIFIED.
TWO COPIES OF THIS CONTRACT
WILL BE SIGNED BY BOTH PARTIES.
AND EACH PARTY
WILL RETAIN A COPY."
IS THIS FOR REAL?
[MINORI, THINKING] WE DIDN'T
HAVE THIS KIND OF SPELL
WHEN WE WERE PLAYING THE GAME.
HE'S MADE A NEW KIND OF MAGIC!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IT STARTED WITH CHIEF
NYANTA'S COOKING SECRET.
IF YOU DO IT FOR YOURSELF
INSTEAD OF RELYING ON THE
SYSTEM TO DO IT FOR YOU,
YOUR FOOD HAS TASTE AS
LONG AS YOUR SKILL LEVEL
IS EQUAL TO THE TASK.
BUT I KNEW IT WASN'T
JUST COOKING THAT
COULD BE MANIPULATED.
WE COULD TAKE IT FURTHER.
[NYANTA] AH, SO YOU'RE TRYING
TO SEE IF YOU CAN GET
THE SAME RESULTS WITH
YOUR SKILLS AS A SCRIBE, HUH?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE FAIRY KING'S PAPER,
MADE FROM THE BEST
INGREDIENTS IN THE GAME,
INK FROM THE TIME DRAGON'S EYE,
AND FINALLY, A CONTRACT
WRITTEN BY A LEVEL 90 SCRIBE...
A NOVEL COMBINATION.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT EFFECT THIS
MAGIC WILL HAVE ON THIS WORLD,
BUT WE'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
[SHIROE] I'VE ALREADY SIGNED IT.
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN.
[RUDY] AN ADVENTURER...
[SHIROE] THIS CONTRACT
CONTAINS AN ELEMENT OF RISK.
YOU'RE GONNA BE A DIFFERENT
TYPE OF BEING FROM WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN USED TO.
YOU SEE, ADVENTURERS ARE
STILL VERY NEW TO THIS WORLD.
AND WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT OUR LIMITATIONS
REALLY ARE, UNDERSTAND?
[SHIROE] IF YOU THINK WE'RE JUST
HERE TO CHASE AFTER GLORY,
YOU MIGHT BE IN FOR A SURPRISE.
I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED THIS.
(ISUZU GASPS)
[RUDY]
AN ADVENTURER'S LIFE...
IF I CAN SAVE PEOPLE
WHO NEED MY HELP,
I DON'T CARE WHAT THE COST IS.
I DON'T WANT THE GLORY.
I WANT TO HELP PEOPLE.
I WANT IT MORE THAN ANYTHING.
(RUNDELLHAUS GASPS)
[ISUZU] IT'S OK.
[RUDY] HUH?
LET ME HELP
YOU, RUDY.
I CAN HELP YOU
WRITE IT.
[BOTH] HM.
(BOTH GASP)
[RUDY] AH!
[SHIROE] OK, IT'S TIME,
RUNDELLHAUS CODE.
TO LIVE LIKE US, YOU NEED
TO DIE LIKE US AT LEAST ONCE.
(MARCHING)
(DIRE WOLVES HOWLING)
(DIRE WOLVES GROWLING)
(YELLING)
(WOLVES ROARING)
(FIRE ROARS)
[TAKAYAMA] A SUMMONED CREATURE
RESTRICTED TO CHARACTERS
LEVEL 86 AND ABOVE...
THE PHOENIX.
(PHOENIX SCREECHES)
(GOBLIN YELLING)
HA! OK, THEN. LET'S SEND
THESE GOBLINS BACK TO HELL.
(GASP)
HYAH!
(ROAR)
(KRUSTY GROWLS)
[TAKAYAMA] THE MAIN
DISH IS FINISHED.
AT THIS POINT, WE CAN LEAVE
THE REST TO THE STRATEGIC
HEADQUARTERS CORDON.
(GASP)
(MARIELLE SIGHS)
[NAOTSUGU] ARE YOU
OK THERE, MARIELLE?
[MARIELLE] HM?
[NAOTSUGU] HM?
(MARIELLE SQUEALS AND SIGHS)
[NAOTSUGU] HM? BECAUSE YOU
DON'T REALLY SEEM OK.
[MARIELLE] IT'S FINE.
I'M JUST REALLY WORN OUT...
OH?
HMM.
HEY, NAOTSUGU.
WHATCHA NEED?
[MARIELLE] WE... WE DID
THE RIGHT THING, RIGHT?
[NAOTSUGU]
OF COURSE WE DID.
WE SAVED A TOWN. THAT SOUNDS
PRETTY GOOD TO ME.
(SNORING)
[MINORI] SHIROE, WHY DID YOU
SAY THAT TO RUNDELLHAUS
BEFORE HE SIGNED THE CONTRACT?
[SHIROE] SAY WHAT?
[MINORI] ABOUT ADVENTURERS NOT
WANTING TO GIVE UP LIVING.
[SHIROE] OH. HMM.
DEFINE "ADVENTURER."
[MINORI] HUH?
WHEN WE WERE ALL
JUST PLAYING THIS,
WE USED THAT WORD TO
DESCRIBE ALL THE PLAYERS.
NOW I'M PRETTY SURE IT SHOULD
STAND FOR SOMETHING ELSE.
I THINK IT'S THE NAME FOR
ALL OF MY COMPANIONS...
EVERYONE WHO WANTS TO TRAVEL
ALL OVER THIS WORLD WITH ME
TO FIND A DAWN
THAT'S STILL UNSEEN.
(BELL RINGING)
(RUDY GROANING)
[RUDY] WHERE AM I?
IS THIS... IT'S GOT TO BE
THE CATHEDRAL, RIGHT?
(GASPS)
"ADVENTURER"!
WOW! I DID IT.
OH, MAN! I'M AN ADVENTURER
JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE.
(HEAVY DOOR OPENS)
[ISUZU] RUDY!
[RUDY] HUH?
[RUDY] AH! MISS ISUZU.
WAIT. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE? OH, I GET IT.
YOU PROBABLY USED A RETURN
SPELL TO GET BACK, RIGHT?
YOU MUST BE THE BIGGEST IDIOT
I'VE EVER MET IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
YOU COULD HAVE DIED, MORON!
WELL, THAT'S KIND OF RUDE.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO BE WILLING
TO MAKE THE ULTIMATE SACRIFICE
FOR YOUR DUTY, MISS ISUZU.
IF I SAY "WAIT,"
YOU WAIT, DUMMY!
WHOA. HEY, LET'S TAKE IT EASY.
I SAID "WAIT"!
[RUDY] AH...
OH, I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I MADE YOU
WORRY BACK THERE, HUH?
AH! OW...
OK? SO I WAS RIGHT. UGH!
I‐I'M SORRY? UGH!
I WON'T DO IT AGAIN,
I PROMISE!
[RUDY] AH!
I GET IT! I GET IT!
I'LL DO WHATEVER
YOU SAY, MISS ISUZU!
JUST STOP HITTING
ME, PLEASE!
[ISUZU] REALLY?
[RUDY] YES. REALLY‐REALLY.
I SWEAR TO GOD.
[ISUZU] AND YOU'RE GONNA
TELL ME ABOUT YOURSELF
AND ABOUT WHEN
YOU WERE A KID.
[RUDY] WHY DO YOU
WANT TO KNOW ABOUT THAT?
(ISUZU GROWLS)
RIGHT. FINE. OK.
I'LL TELL YOU.
[ISUZU] AND THE NEXT TIME YOU
PULL A CRAZY STUNT LIKE THAT,
I'LL MAKE SURE YOU
WON'T LIVE THROUGH IT.
[RUDY]
I'LL REMEMBER THAT.
[ISUZU] GIVE ME YOUR PAW.
[RUDY] HUH?
(ISUZU CHUCKLES)
(RUDY CHUCKLES)
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
THE BATTLE HAS ENDED.
EASTAL AND THE ROUND TABLE
TAKE A NEW STEP FORWARD.
TO CELEBRATE THEIR VICTORY,
A BALL IS HELD.
BUT NOT EVERYONE IS
FEELING A SENSE OF CHEER.
FALL IS COMING TO THE
TOWN OF AKIHABARA,
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] WE WILL
CHANGE THE WORLD.