(MARIELLE GASPS) THE SECOND
GROUP OF INSTRUCTORS IS HERE.
THIS SUMMER CAMP IS TOTALLY
GOING OFF WITHOUT A HITCH.
I'M SO HAPPY.
(WATER FLOWING)
[MINORI] SERIOUSLY.
LET'S USE THE EXTRA TIME
TO DISCUSS OUR STRATEGY
AND GO A LITTLE LATER.
NOW, LOOK HERE, MINORI.
WHAT IN THE WORLD DO YOU THINK
WE'RE DOING OUT HERE ANYWAY?
WE NEED TO GET AS MUCH
EXPERIENCE AS WE CAN
TO RAISE OUR LEVELS,
AND WE NEED TO GO TO
THE DUNGEON TO DO THAT.
OF COURSE. BUT HERE'S THE
THING ABOUT IT...
WE'VE BARELY LASTED
3 HOURS A DAY IN THERE.
OK... WHAT'S
YOUR POINT?
MY POINT IS IF WE'RE ONLY
GOING TO LAST THAT LONG,
WE MIGHT AS WELL GO LATER IN THE
DAY SINCE WE'RE GETTING BEAT.
YEAH? AND
WHY IS THAT?
BECAUSE WE HAVEN'T WORKED
OUT A STRATEGY YET!
[SERARA] MINORI‐CHAN...
[RUDY] SO WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO THIS MORNING?
[MINORI] LET'S TRY TAKING
IT EASY FOR A CHANGE.
[RUDY] MISS MINORI, YOU
CANNOT BE SERIOUS ABOUT THAT!
[ISUZU] CALM DOWN, RUDY.
SHE'S SERIOUS.
I THINK SHE MIGHT BE ON
TO SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
[RUDY] UHH.
[MINORI] I DIDN'T EXACTLY
MEAN TAKE IT EASY, ANYWAY.
BUT WE NEED TO TAKE THE
TIME TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
WE DID THAT.
WE ALREADY INTRODUCED
OURSELVES TO EACH OTHER.
OH NO, WE DIDN'T.
WHAT?
NOT IN A WAY THAT COUNTS.
NOT REALLY.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ALL THAT
HELPFUL ABOUT ANY OF YOU.
YOUR LIKES AND DISLIKES...
WHAT YOUR CONCERNS ARE.
[MINORI] I DON'T KNOW IF YOU
WANT TO STAND AT THE FRONT
OR STAY AT THE BACK
OF THE FORMATION.
KNOWING THESE THINGS IS
IMPORTANT IF YOU WANT
ME TO HELP, ANYWAY.
SO, LET ME KNOW.
I'M NOT THAT POWERFUL,
AND I CAN'T REALLY HELP YOU,
NOT UNLESS YOU
TELL ME EVERYTHING.
AND WHEN I SAY
EVERYTHING, I MEAN IT.
EVERYTHING?
EVERY LITTLE DETAIL.
OK. LET ME GIVE
YOU AN EXAMPLE.
WHAT'S THE NAME OF
YOUR FIRE MAGIC?
HMM. IT IS THE ORB OF LAVA.
AMAZING. AN INCREDIBLE
BALL OF MOLTEN MAGMA.
[MINORI] RIGHT. SO THAT
REALLY DOESN'T TELL ME
ANYTHING ABOUT IT,
OTHER THAN YOU LIKE IT.
RUNDELLHAUS, WHY DO YOU USE
THE ORB OF LAVA INSTEAD
OF ANYTHING ELSE?
WHY DO YOU KEEP
USING IT INSTEAD OF
SOME OF YOUR OTHER
ATTACK SPELLS?
I USE IT BECAUSE IT'S
EXTREMELY EFFECTIVE, OK?
AND WHY IS
IT EFFECTIVE?
HUH.
OH, COME ON NOW.
IT IS WITHOUT A DOUBT ONE
OF THE MOST POWERFUL SPELLS
I'VE EVER MASTERED.
MY CASTING TIME
IS REALLY INSANE.
TWO SECONDS AND IT'S GONE.
THAT AND ITS
COOL‐DOWN TIME IS 18.
SERIOUSLY, I COULD JUST
STAND THERE AND CAST IT
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
I MEAN, IT'S A MAJOR ATTACK
SPELL I COULD CAST EVERY
20 SECONDS, ALL THE TIME.
NOW, HANG ON A SECOND...
ONE OF THE WAYS A SAMURAI
GETS THINGS DONE IS
BY TAUNTING HIS FOES.
NEVER HEARD OF
THAT BEFORE.
[TOYA] YEAH. TAUNTS
DISTRACT THE ENEMY.
WHEN THEY'RE PROVOKED,
I CAN HIT THEM WITH AN ATTACK,
LIKE THE THUNDER SLASH,
WHICH IS POWERFUL.
BUT IT'S ONLY GOOD
FOR 3 METERS.
ANOTHER ATTACK OF MINE,
THE SAMURAI'S CHALLENGE,
HAS EVEN LESS RANGE.
[RUDY] OK, SO
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
THEY'RE JUST EXAMPLES OF
WAYS TO TAUNT THE ENEMY.
THEY DON'T ACTUALLY DO
ANY REAL DAMAGE OR ANYTHING
DURING THE FIGHT,
BUT AN ENEMY OF LOW INTELLIGENCE
WILL THINK THAT THEY'VE TAKEN
A WHOLE BUNCH OF HITS.
LIKE SKELETONS?
YOU USE TAUNTS TO
DRAW THEIR ATTENTION?
THAT'S RIGHT. THE SAMURAI
HAS HIGH DEFENSIVE
CAPABILITY IN A FIGHT.
SO I'M SUPPOSED TO KEEP
THEM FOCUSED ON ME INSTEAD
OF THE REST OF YOU.
[TOYA] NOW, SAMURAI'S CHALLENGE
TAKES TWO SECONDS TO LAND.
THAT'S JUST LIKE
RUDY'S ORB OF LAVA.
BUT IT DOESN'T AFFECT ANYTHING
PAST THE REACH OF MY SWORD.
[RUDY] RIGHT.
I GET IT.
IF BOTH OF US ATTACK
AT THE VERY SAME TIME
WHEN WE'RE IN RANGE
OF THE ENEMY.
MM‐HMM. YOUR ORB OF LAVA
WILL HIT THE ATTACKING
SKELETONS FIRST.
AND THEN WE END UP LOSING
THE ADVANTAGE OF HAVING
THEM COME AFTER ME.
AND THAT'S WHY ALL THE ENEMIES
HAVE BEEN GOING AFTER YOU.
SO THEN YOU'RE TRYING TO
TELL ME NOT TO USE IT?!
I'M TELLING YOU TO
WAIT TWO SECONDS!
THE LOSS OF TWO
SECONDS CAN BE FATAL
IN A GLORIOUS,
ELEGANT BATTLE!
[ISUZU] OK, LET ME THINK...
I'VE GOT SOMETHING
I'D LIKE TO TRY OUT...
THE FUGUE OF COWARDS.
WHAT IS THAT?
[RUDY] SOUNDS COWARDLY,
JUDGING BY THE NAME.
IS THAT A SKILL
OF YOURS, MISS ISUZU?
[ISUZU] WELL, THE FUGUE OF
COWARDS IS A DEFENSE SONG
THAT I JUST PICKED UP.
IT'S A SONG THAT PROVIDES
CONTINUOUS SUPPORT.
[SERARA] IT'S CONTINUOUS?
[ISUZU] IN OTHER WORDS,
IT KEEPS ON GOING AFTER
I START PLAYING IT.
IF YOU HAPPEN TO BE
A NON‐WARRIOR CLASS,
THE FUGUE OF COWARDS
MAKES THE DAMAGE YOU DEAL
APPEAR LOWER THAN
IT ACTUALLY IS
AND THE ENEMY MISJUDGES
ITS STRENGTH.
[TOYA] YOU HAVE
A SKILL LIKE THAT?
[RUDY]
SERIOUSLY?
[ISUZU] SURE,
BUT YOU KNOW,
I JUST LEARNED IT, SO,
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S ALL
THAT AMAZING, REALLY.
I MEAN, IT SOUNDS USELESS.
IT DOESN'T DO ANY
DAMAGE TO THE ENEMY
AND IT DOESN'T SEEM
TO HELP TO HEAL ANYBODY.
[TOYA] NO, IT'S GREAT.
[RUDY] YOU KNOW,
THAT COULD BE REALLY HELPFUL.
I'M GLAD YOU SAID
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
MISS MINORI, IT WOULD
APPEAR I MIGHT OWE YOU
A BIT OF AN APOLOGY.
I HUMBLY ADMIT MY IGNORANCE,
LACK OF UNDERSTANDING,
AND FOOLISHNESS.
IT'S FINE. IT'S NOT LIKE I
UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING, EITHER.
SO, THEN, LET'S TAKE SOME TIME
AND GO OVER ALL THE SPELLS
YOU KNOW, RUNDELLHAUS.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE AND
DISLIKE ABOUT THEM?
WHEN DO YOU USE THEM?
WHEN WOULD YOU
LIKE TO USE THEM?
TELL YOU ALL OF THEM?
THAT'S GONNA TAKE A LOT
OF TIME, MISS MINORI.
WE JUST MADE
THE TIME, RUDY.
SO TELL US ABOUT IT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
LET'S HEAR 'EM!
OK. LET'S START WITH
WHAT YOU ALREADY TOLD ME
AND WORK THROUGH THE
REST OF WHAT YOU GOT.
THEIR PATROL'S
COMING UP, GUYS.
[ISUZU] LOOKS LIKE THERE'S FIVE.
THEY'LL BE HERE IN
ABOUT 10 MEASURES.
[TOYA, THINKING]
OK. 10 MEASURES IS...
ABOUT 20 SECONDS.
LET'S DO THIS
LIKE WE SAID.
[TOYA, THINKING]
IT'LL BE FINE. I CAN DO THIS.
[SERARA, THINKING] YESTERDAY,
WE SPENT ALL DAY TALKING
INSTEAD OF GOING
INTO THE DUNGEON.
[ISUZU, THINKING] I KNOW
WHAT EVERYONE'S SKILLS ARE
AND WE CAN MAKE
THEM WORK TOGETHER.
[RUDY, THINKING]
I SPENT A LOT OF VALUABLE TIME
LISTENING TO WHAT EVERYBODY SAID
ABOUT OUR TALENTS YESTERDAY.
THIS HAD BETTER WORK.
[MINORI, THINKING]
NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
PUT EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
[MINORI] FORMATION STYLE,
THE OPERATOR, THE FIELD
MONITOR, AND PATROL COLUMN.
SO, THE NEXT THING
WE HAVE TO DO
IS MEMORIZE THE BASICS OF
PARTY COMBAT I JUST WENT OVER.
[RUDY] I'VE
GOT IT IN MY HEAD,
BUT WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO WITH IT NOW THAT I
KNOW ABOUT IT, MINORI?
[MINORI] WELL, IT'S LIKE THIS.
[TOYA] CONTACT!
[MINORI] HUH?
[TOYA] LIGHTNING SLASH!
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER] YOU HAVE
TO BE FAMILIAR WITH YOUR
PARTY'S FORMATION FIRST.
THE BASIC IDEA IS THAT OUR
FRONT‐LINE FIGHTER, OUR SAMURAI,
WILL DRAW THE ENEMY'S ATTACKS.
BUT IF HE DOESN'T GET
SUPPORT FROM THE REST OF US,
HE'S IN BIG TROUBLE.
OK, GUYS, WHENEVER YOU'RE READY!
[ISUZU] UHH!
[MINORI] UHH! OH... OH, UHH.
[RUDY] GET BACK!
UHH! ALL RIGHT,
LOOK HERE, SKINNY...
I'M NOT GONNA WASTE AN ORB OF
LAVA ON JUST ONE OF YOU LOSERS.
LET'S DO THIS!
A LITTLE BIT MORE
ELEGANTLY THIS TIME.
LIGHTNING CHAMBER!
[TOYA] YEAH! UHH!
AAH! BACK OFF! UHH!
TOYA'S HP IS DOWN TO 64%!
HE NEEDS SOME HEALING!
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
ONCE YOU KNOW YOUR FORMATION,
YOU HAVE TO WORK
WITH YOUR OPERATOR.
THE OPERATOR MONITORS
EVERYONE'S STATUS,
AND SINCE IT'S A WASTE OF
TIME FOR ME AND SERARA
TO CAST HEALING SPELLS
AT THE SAME TIME,
I CAN FILL THAT ROLE
AND KEEP AN EYE ON
WHO NEEDS HELP OUT THERE.
THANKS A LOT!
I NEEDED THAT! UHH!
[TOYA, THINKING] OH, MAN.
THIS IS REALLY STARTING TO HURT.
[NAOTSUGU] YOUR JOB
AS A FRONT‐LINE TANK
IS TO ABSORB ALL THE ENEMY HITS
AND TRUST YOUR COMPANIONS
TO HAVE YOUR BACK.
TOYA, AS A MAN, YOU GOTTA
PROMISE TO BE AWESOME.
[TOYA] I DIDN'T FORGET,
MASTER NAOTSUGU.
RIGHT. YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME?!
SAMURAI'S CHALLENGE!
UHH! UHH!
MINORI, WATCH MY BACK!
I'M GONNA NEED SOME
HEAVY‐DUTY MAGIC, YOU GUYS!
[ISUZU AND MINORI] RIGHT!
[RUDY] YEAH!
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
IN THIS CASE, I'M ALSO
THE FIELD MONITOR.
AN OPERATOR KEEPS AN EYE
ON THE PARTY'S HEALTH,
BUT A FIELD MONITOR WATCHES OVER
CHANGING BATTLEFIELD CONDITIONS,
ALLOWING THE PARTY
TO CONTINUE FIGHTING.
CHECKING AHEAD! I DON'T SEE ANY
ENEMY PATROLS IN THE CORRIDOR!
THEY DON'T HAVE BACKUP.
GO AHEAD AND ENGAGE!
DID YOU MANAGE TO GET
THEM ALL MAD AT US?
[TOYA] NO. I HAD TO USE
SAMURAI'S CHALLENGE
TWICE ON ALL OF THEM.
NOW THEY DEFINITELY WANT TO
BEAT ON ME INSTEAD OF YOU GUYS.
OK. LET'S TEST THAT
DISTRACTION OF YOURS.
[ISUZU] BEAT OF RESONANCE!
ORB OF LAVA!
ALL RIGHT. IT'S TIME TO
SEND YOU BACK TO THE
DARKNESS YOU CAME FROM!
YAH!
[TOYA] AWESOME!
[RUDY] FRIGID WIND!
[ISUZU] OHH.
REINFORCED RECTANGLE!
LET'S GET OUR
PATROL FILE GOING!
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER] CALLING
A SPECIFIC PATROL FILE
ALLOWS EVERYONE
TO WATCH OVERLAPPING
PARTS OF THE BATTLE AREA.
IT ALSO PUTS HEALERS AND
FIGHTERS IN THE RIGHT PLACE
IN CASE A PARTY
GETS ATTACKED AGAIN.
THE IDEA HERE IS
TO BE ABLE TO SEE
WHAT SOMEONE ELSE
MIGHT NOT BE ABLE TO.
[RUDY] SO, DID WE TRIUMPH?
I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING ELSE.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE REALLY DID!
[TOYA] ALL RIGHT!
(ISUZU LAUGHS)
[SERARA] WE DID IT!
HUH. NOW THAT'S
HOW WE DO IT, GUYS.
YOU SEE, MAN, I TOLD YA!
IT TOTALLY WORKED!
(LAUGHTER)
[MINORI, THINKING]
BROTHER SHIROE, I GET IT NOW.
WE JUST NEEDED TO TALK TO EACH
OTHER AND WORK THINGS OUT.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE
LITTLE THINGS THAT'S MORE
IMPORTANT THAN ANYTHING.
AND IT MADE OUR IMPROVISED PARTY
A REAL GROUP OF TRUE FRIENDS.
[HENRIETTA] THANKS SO MUCH.
WRITING ON THIS WORLD'S
PAPER IS CHALLENGING.
YOU CAN TAKE AS
MUCH AS YOU NEED.
MAKING PAPER AND INK
IS SORT OF IN THE JOB
DESCRIPTION OF A SCRIBE.
BUT I STILL NEED SOME
PRACTICE MAKING THE INK.
WELL, NOW. IF THIS BATCH
IS ANYTHING LIKE THE LAST,
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO WORK THAT HARD.
WRITING WITH IT ISN'T
MY ONLY OBJECTIVE.
[HENRIETTA] HUH?
[SHIROE] BACK WHEN
YOU WERE PLAYING,
DIDN'T YOU HAVE ANY
MISSIONS WHERE THE
QUALITY OF YOUR DOCUMENTS
AFFECTED THE OUTCOME
OF YOUR QUEST?
WELL, I GUESS I DID.
[SHIROE] A SINGLE DOCUMENT
CAN BE A MAGICAL ITEM,
AND IF YOU WANT THE
DOCUMENT TO BE EFFECTIVE,
YOU HAVE TO COMPOSE IT WITH MORE
HIGHLY‐REFINED INK AND PAPER.
WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE.
SO, YOU'RE COPYING THIS MAP TO
RAISE YOUR SKILL IN CARTOGRAPHY.
[SHIROE] NO. I JUST
NEED A BETTER COPY.
ALL THESE PAPYRUS
AND TREE BARK MAPS
KEEP FALLING APART ON ME
BEFORE I'M DONE WITH THEM.
[HENRIETTA] YOU LOOK TIRED.
[SHIROE] HMM.
[HENRIETTA] MAKING ALL THIS
HAPPEN REALLY IS A LOT OF
WORK FOR YOU, AM I RIGHT?
[SHIROE] YEAH, I DON'T
THINK THAT'S THE REASON.
[HENRIETTA] HMM?
[SHIROE] UH, WHAT I MEAN
IS MAYBE I'M TIRED FROM
THE DANCE LAST NIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, MAYBE THE
TWO OF US SHOULD GET IN A
LITTLE MORE PRACTICE TIME
IN CASE THEY HAVE
ANOTHER EVENT.
[SHIROE] I'M GOOD. REALLY.
[HENRIETTA] ANYTIME YOU WANT TO,
JUST GET IN TOUCH WITH ME.
THANKS AGAIN FOR YOUR HELP.
I LOOK TIRED? YEAH...
I GUESS SHE COULD BE RIGHT.
MAYBE I'M THINKING WAY
TOO MUCH ABOUT THIS.
HMM.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] EVERY TIME
WE DIE IN THIS WORLD,
WE LOSE OUR MEMORIES.
SO DOES THAT MEAN...
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT WE
COULD FORGET THE REAL WORLD?
[SHIROE, THINKING]
THERE'S SO MUCH WE DON'T
KNOW ABOUT THIS WORLD.
WE CAN'T JUST ASSUME
THERE'S A COMFY CHAIR
AND A SNACK WAITING
FOR US AFTERWARDS.
(BEEPING)
HUH?
(CHIME)
[MINORI] GOOD EVENING,
BROTHER SHIROE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SO, HOW DID IT GO IN THE
DUNGEON FOR YOU GUYS? OK?
[MINORI] HA! YOU ALREADY
KNOW, DON'T YOU?
WELL, YEAH.
BUT YOU SOUND REALLY HAPPY.
OH. I AM.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE REPORT.
WE MET TO DISCUSS OUR STRATEGY
AT AROUND 7:30 THIS MORNING.
WE EXPLORED SEVERAL
OPTIONS AND THEN MADE
OUR WAY TO THE DUNGEON.
WE GOT AS FAR AS THE
END OF THE RIGHT FORK,
AND THEN WE DEFEATED THE BURNING
DEAD AT THE BLAST FURNACE.
NOW THAT'S AMAZING!
BEATING THE BURNING DEAD IS
STILL A PRETTY BIG CHALLENGE
FOR THE SKILL LEVEL
IN YOUR PARTY.
IT'S ONE THING TO
DO IT IN THE GAME,
BUT MAKING THAT WORK WITH A
VETERAN PARTY IS NOT THAT EASY.
YEAH.
[SHIROE] AND THE REST?
UH, THEY'RE ALL IN
THE TENT RIGHT NOW.
[SHIROE] HA. THAT'S
NOT WHAT I MEANT.
HOW DID THEY DO OUT THERE?
[MINORI] WELL, LET'S SEE.
TOYA GOT TO THE
FRONT OF THE PARTY
AND DREW THE
ENEMY'S ATTENTION,
WHICH IS WHAT YOU'VE
ALWAYS TOLD ME TO DO.
BUT THIS TIME WE SET
OUR POSITIONS IN THE
FORMATION IN ADVANCE.
WE ALSO MADE SURE WE
STUCK TO SMALLER CHAMBERS.
THAT WAY, WE COULD FIGHT THE
ENEMY PATROLS ON OUR OWN TERMS.
SO YOU WERE FUNNELING.
[MINORI] RIGHT. WE MADE SURE
WE ELIMINATED THE ENEMIES
WITH RANGED ATTACKS FIRST.
I LET SERARA HANDLE THE HEALING
SO I COULD MONITOR EVERYONE
AND WATCH THE BATTLEFIELD.
AND WE ALSO ELIMINATED
ONE ENEMY AT A TIME
INSTEAD OF LETTING
THEM HEAL UP.
DID THAT MAKE ANY SENSE?
[SHIROE] YOU'RE DOING
FINE. REALLY.
[SHIROE, THINKING] IT'S LIKE
I CAN SEE THEM IN MY HEAD.
THEY'VE FINALLY MASTERED
THE BASICS I GAVE MINORI
AND STARTED IMPLEMENTING
TEAMWORK TO PULL
IT ALL TOGETHER.
IT SEEMS OBVIOUS,
BUT NOT EVERYONE DOES IT.
THERE ARE SO MANY LITTLE
THINGS YOU HAVE TO GET RIGHT
OR IT JUST DOESN'T WORK.
[MINORI] UM, BROTHER SHIROE?
CAN YOU STILL HEAR ME?
[SHIROE] OH, YEAH.
I CAN HEAR YOU FINE.
EVERYONE DID THEIR PART?
[MINORI] OH, YEAH. SERARA HAS
A LOT OF DIFFERENT SPELLS
AND THEY'RE ALL AMAZING.
I'M GLAD SHE'S DOING
MOST OF THE HEALING.
BUT ALL THE DIFFERENT THINGS
ISUZU CAN DO IS CRAZY.
IT'S A REAL CHORE TO
REMEMBER ALL OF THEM.
(SHIROE LAUGHS)
[MINORI] UH, SHIROE?
ARE YOU LAUGHING?
SORRY. I'M NOT. REALLY. HONEST.
OUR SORCERER, RUNDELLHAUS...
EVERYONE'S STARTING
TO CALL HIM RUDY NOW.
HE'S GETTING BETTER
ALL THE TIME.
HE'S A BIT OF A PRETTY BOY.
[RUDY] HUH?!
[MINORI] BUT CAN BE SORT
OF A BONEHEAD SOMETIMES.
[SHIROE] HA HA! SO HE'S HANDSOME
BUT NOT THAT BRIGHT. GOT IT.
YEAH, BUT HE'S GOOD
TO HAVE AROUND,
EVEN IF HE'S KIND
OF FULL OF IT.
ANYWAY, HIS MAGIC
IS REALLY POWERFUL.
WE'RE LUCKY TO HAVE HIM.
(SHIROE LAUGHS)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] WE STILL
HAVE A LOT TO LEARN ABOUT HOW
THIS WORLD REALLY WORKS.
BUT IT WON'T HAPPEN ALL AT ONCE.
I JUST NEED TO REMEMBER TO
STAY POSITIVE, LIKE MINORI.
I'LL GET THIS DONE,
ONE THING AT A TIME.
YOU'VE INCONVENIENCED ME,
MASTER KRUSTY.
I HAVE?
YOU'VE ASSUMED YOU COULD
JUST CALL ME OUT HERE.
A REAL INVITATION FROM
A GENTLEMAN REQUIRES GRACE.
NOT JUST "HEY, LADY,
COME AND SEE ME."
[KRUSTY] HONESTLY,
I THOUGHT YOU'D LIKE THIS.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
YOU ALWAYS STRUCK
ME AS A PERSON
WITH A CERTAIN DISDAIN
FOR FORMALITY.
LIKE OUR NAP
THE OTHER DAY.
[RAYNESHIA] UH...
LOOKS LIKE I WAS
RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
MAY I INVITE YOU
AGAIN TOMORROW?
[RAYNESHIA] AS YOU LIKE.
[KRUSTY] HUH?
I SAID "AS YOU LIKE."
OH, MAN, THIS IS
SO MUCH BETTER.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GONNA
TAKE FOREVER TO WASH
ALL OF THAT DUNGEON STINK OFF.
IT GETS A LITTLE DIRTY
IN THERE, THAT'S FOR SURE.
I GUESS OUR PARTY
MANAGED TO HAVE
A PRETTY GOOD SHOWING
TODAY, DIDN'T WE?
YEAH. I KINDA
GOT A LITTLE WORRIED
THERE FOR A WHILE WHEN MORE OF
THE BURNING DEAD SHOWED UP.
BUT IT TURNED OUT
OK IN THE END.
YOU AND RUDY WORKED
REALLY WELL TOGETHER.
SO, I GUESS I SHOULD BE
HAPPY ABOUT THAT, SHOULDN'T I?
OH, I'D SAY YOU SHOULD BE
MORE THAN HAPPY WITH IT.
[MINORI] DIDN'T YOU SAY
RUDY SEEMS LIKE SOME
KIND OF A PRINCE,
OR WERE YOU JOKING?
[ISUZU] WELL, YEAH, BUT
DON'T YOU THINK SO, TOO?
I MEAN, KINDA, RIGHT?
LIKE, IF YOU DIDN'T
ALREADY KNOW HIM,
AND YOU RAN INTO HIM
SOMEWHERE ELSE,
WOULDN'T YOU THINK HE'S CUTE?
I MEAN...
SO YOU THINK
HE'S CUTE.
NO! NO WAY!
[ISUZU] WELL,
MAYBE A LITTLE.
(ISUZU PLAYING LUTE)
COME ON. IT WASN'T WORTH
ANY APPLAUSE, WAS IT?
NO, IT WAS WONDERFUL.
YOUR PLAYING WENT SO FAR AS TO
BECOME ONE WITH THE AIR ITSELF.
THANK YOU.
[ISUZU] I WONDER IF EVERYONE'S
GETTING READY TO SLEEP.
[RUDY] WE'RE GETTING
UP PRETTY EARLY TOMORROW.
OUR MORNING SESSION IS
GONNA BE OUR LAST RUN
THROUGH THE DUNGEON.
YEAH, IT IS.
TRAINING SURE
WENT FAST.
IT'S BEEN FUN, RIGHT?
[RUDY] YEAH.
FOOD WASN'T BAD,
BUT IT COULD'VE
BEEN BETTER.
OH, REALLY?
I KIND OF
ENJOYED IT...
BARBECUE AND STUFF.
WHAT DO YOU NORMALLY HAVE?
EITHER A HOT SANDWICH,
OR A HOT SANDWICH...
OR A SANDWICH...
AND THEN I BET
ANOTHER HOT SANDWICH?
HEY, I DON'T
SUPPOSE YOU MEAN
THE RAY PARKER POLLOCK
ROE SANDWICHES.
WHOA! HOW THE
HECK DID YOU‐
YOU LIKE CAVIAR
SANDWICHES?
THEY'RE AWESOME!
I LOVE HOW THEY POP
WHEN YOU BITE INTO THEM.
AHH! I LOVE
THE POPPING THING!
(PANTING)
(ISUZU LAUGHING)
[ISUZU, THINKING]
ARE YOU KIDDING?!
(DOG BARKS)
HE'S LIKE A DOG,
A GOLDEN RETRIEVER!
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU DOING OK?
[ISUZU] NO, I'M FINE.
NOTHING'S WRONG AT ALL.
[ISUZU, THINKING] I GET IT.
THAT'S WHY I'VE NEVER BEEN
NERVOUS AROUND HIM.
HE'S CUTE.
(DOG BARKS)
BUT HE'S CUTE
LIKE A DOG!
(GIGGLES)
[RUDY] ARE YOU CRYING?
(ISUZU GIGGLES)
[RUDY] IS IT BECAUSE
WE'RE GONNA BE SEPARATED
AFTER THE CAMP'S OVER?
YEAH, THAT JUST MIGHT BE IT.
BUT YOU KNOW, I COULD SEE
YOU ANY TIME IF I WANTED TO
IF YOU WERE IN A GUILD.
SO THAT'S IT. JUST HAVE
ME HOOK UP WITH A GUILD?
IT WOULD DEFINITELY
BE A HEINOUS CRIME
TO CONFINE A TALENT
SUCH AS MINE
TO A SOLITARY GROUP
OF ADVENTURERS.
(ISUZU GIGGLES)
[ISUZU, THINKING] HOW CAN HE
WINK SO NATURALLY LIKE THAT?
HE REALLY IS AMAZING.
(DOG BARKS)
BUT HE'S A DOG!
BEING A FREE AGENT
ISN'T A BAD THING.
I'M SURE THERE'S
A LOT OF GROUPS
THAT'LL WANT ME TO
GO ALONG WITH THEM.
EVEN AFTER THIS LITTLE
TRAINING CAMP ENDS,
YOU'LL SURELY HEAR
RUMORS OF MY EXPLOITS
IN AND AROUND AKIHABARA.
AND, OF COURSE, YOU CAN
FEEL FREE TO CONTACT
ME WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
WELL, I CAN'T ARGUE
WITH THAT, NOW CAN I?
LET ME JUST CALL
THE HEADS UP DISPLAY
AND ADD YOU TO
MY FRIENDS LIST.
UH.
[ISUZU] YOU'RE BUYING THE FIRST
HOT FISH EGG SANDWICH, THOUGH.
AND YOU'RE IN. UH... OK.
(BEEPING)
WELL, THAT'S WEIRD.
[RUDY] HMM.
(EXPLOSION)
(ROARING)
[SHIGERU] SAHUAGIN?!
THE FISH MONSTERS?!
[SHORYU] THAT'S RIGHT.
MARIELLE SAID THEY
APPEARED ON THE COAST.
[SHIGERU] OK, GOT IT.
SAHUAGIN SHOULD BE
LEVEL 20 TO 30 AT MOST.
THE NEW KIDS OUGHT TO BE
ABLE TO HANDLE THEM.
THEY'RE NOT REALLY
THAT TOUGH.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
UHH!
(ROARING)
THAT'S A
LOT OF FISH.
THIS IS
RIDICULOUS.
[SHORYU] I'VE NEVER SEEN
THAT MANY AT ONCE.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(SWORDS CLASHING)
GET OFF THE BEACH!
GET INTO THE TREE LINE!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
[MARIELLE] AAH!
UHH. OOH.
[SHORYU] MARIELLE! UHH!
[MARIELLE] SHORYU!
[SHORYU] STAY BACK! UHH! AHH!
WE HAVE TO CALL THE GROUPS
CAMPING IN THE FOREST!
(ROARING)
[MARIELLE] ARE YOU SURE?
[SHORYU] I'M YOUR COMBAT LEADER
AND WE ARE IN COMBAT!
PLEASE DO WHAT I TELL YOU!
[MARIELLE] FINE, WHATEVER.
(SCOFFS)
[SHORYU] UHH!
[MARIELLE] UHH!
WHERE DID ALL THESE
NASTY FISHY MEN COME FROM?!
[SHORYU] AAH!
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
A SUDDEN ASSAULT BY DEMI‐HUMANS.
HUGE ARMIES OF GOBLINS
AND SAHUAGIN.
YET STILL, THE PEOPLE
OF THE LANDS' NOBLES
AND THE ROUND TABLE MEMBERS
CANNOT PUT ASIDE THEIR
DIFFERENCES AND WORK TOGETHER.
MEANWHILE, TOYA, MINORI, AND THE
OTHER YOUNG PLAYERS TAKE ACTION.
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.