[REGAN] NOW, THAT'S STRANGE...
[AKATSUKI] THIS IS EVEN
MORE AMAZING THAN
YOUR STUDY, MY LORD.
SO SORRY ABOUT THIS.
I COULD HAVE SWORN I
HAD A COUPLE OF VIALS
FOR US TO DRINK FROM
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
[SHIROE] IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[REGAN] HUH? HMM.
[SHIROE] TRY THIS.
(REGAN SLURPS) HMM.
BY THE WAY, ISN'T THAT
DAZANEGG'S MAGIC BAG?
I BELIEVE YOU NEED
A PURPLE FLAME CRYSTAL
AND THE SKIN OF A WINGED
DRAGON TO MAKE ONE.
RIGHT.
I QUESTED FOR THE ITEMS,
AND THEN I HAD SOMEONE
MAKE IT FOR ME.
[SHIROE, THINKING] HE KNOWS
ALL THE REQUIREMENTS
FOR THE LEVEL 45 QUEST,
"GET THE MAGIC BAG."
EVERYONE DOES IT EVENTUALLY.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
[TOYA] TOMORROW, WE'LL GO
IN THE AFTERNOON.
[ALL] RIGHT.
[TOYA] AS LONG AS WE GET
AT LEAST AN HOUR'S REST,
WE SHOULD COMPLETELY
RESTORE OUR POINTS.
[RUDY] YUP.
[SERARA] OK. BUT
THEY'RE ONLY GONNA
LET US INTO THE DUNGEON
ONCE A DAY ANYWAY.
[NAOTSUGU] THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
[TOYA] MASTER NAOTSUGU!
AND IF YOU TRY GOING
BACK IN, WE'LL SEND
YOU BACK TO AKIHABARA.
[RUDY] BUT MASTER!
[NAOTSUGU] ADVENTURERS
SHOULD FOLLOW THE RULES
SET DOWN FOR THEM ALL THE TIME.
PART OF YOUR JOB IS ENSURING
YOU GET ENOUGH REST.
(TOYA GRUMBLES)
(MINORI WHIMPERS SOFTLY)
[REGAN] I'M SORRY.
BACK AT THE PALACE,
I REFERRED TO
MYSELF AS A MAGE.
HOWEVER, IT MIGHT BE
MORE PRECISE TO SAY
I AM A PRACTITIONER
OF MAGICAL SCIENCES.
[SHIROE] HMM.
THE MAGICIAN OF MIRROR LAKE,
AT YOUR SERVICE, SIR.
REGAN.
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU SAYING YOU'RE
THE MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE?
[AKATSUKI] DO YOU KNOW
OF HIM, MY LORD?
WHEN I WAS PLAYING,
HIS NAME CAME UP A LOT
IN TOWN RUMORS AND IN
THE DESCRIPTIONS OF
A FEW OF THE QUESTS.
FOR EXAMPLE, THE MAIN ITEM
FOR THE 9 DUNGEONS
OF THE HALOS RAID,
THE KEY OF ETERNAL DARKNESS,
WAS SAID TO HAVE BEEN
MADE BY SOMEONE CALLED
THE MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE.
HMM.
[SHIROE] YOU KNOW AS WELL AS
I DO THAT GAME DEVELOPERS
WILL CREATE A NAME FOR A
PERSON THAT YOU NEVER SEE
TO MAKE A QUEST
MORE INTERESTING.
I DIDN'T THINK HE WAS REAL.
I GAINED THE TITLE MYSELF
FROM MY OLD MASTER,
BUT I REALLY HADN'T BEEN
USING IT MUCH SINCE THEN.
[SHIROE] SO THEN,
YOU INHERITED THE NAME
"THE MAGE OF MIRROR LAKE"?
[REGAN] CORRECT.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
WOW. I CAN'T BEGIN TO DESCRIBE
HOW IMPORTANT THIS GUY IS.
THIS IS AN AMAZING CHANCE
TO LEARN HOW THIS WORLD WORKS.
[REGAN] MAGIC IS A
CURIOUS THING, MY FRIEND.
WIDELY VARIED WITH MANY TYPES.
MY OWN SPECIALTY IS
A LITTLE SOMETHING
THAT I LIKE TO REFER TO
AS "WORLD CLASS" MAGIC
AND ENCHANTMENTS.
[SHIROE] "WORLD CLASS"?
I'M NOT FAMILIAR WITH IT.
[REGAN] LET'S FIRST
CLASSIFY MAGIC
BY THE SPELL'S
AREA OF EFFECT.
ACTION CLASS, COMBAT CLASS,
OPERATION CLASS,
TACTICAL CLASS,
STRATEGY, NATIONAL DEFENSE
CLASS, CONTINENT CLASS,
AND FINALLY,
THERE'S WORLD CLASS.
[SHIROE] ISN'T MAGIC
USUALLY DIVIDED BY TYPE?
[REGAN] TRUE, BUT WHEN YOU
CONSIDER THE SCALE OF A SPELL,
YOU START ALLOWING
YOURSELF TO UNDERSTAND
HOW IT WORKS FROM A PERSPECTIVE
OF NUMBERS OF PERSONS AFFECTED,
OR SPECIFICALLY, THE
PHENOMENOLOGICAL PERSPECTIVE.
ACTION CLASS MAGIC
REFERS TO THOSE SPELLS
THAT REPLICATE OR REPLACE
A SINGLE PHYSICAL ACTION
WITH AN ENERGETIC RESPONSE.
FOR EXAMPLE, SWINGING A SWORD
AND FIGHTING A MONSTER.
THE ACTION CLASS EQUIVALENT
IS A LIGHTNING BOLT.
COMBAT CLASS MAGIC IS
CAPABLE OF ALTERING
THE OVERALL OUTCOME
OF A SINGLE BATTLE.
ANY SPELL THAT CAN
ATTACK OR STRIKE DOWN
LARGE MOBS OR ENTIRE
COMBAT TEAMS OF ENEMIES
IS COMBAT CLASS.
AND THEN THERE'S
OPERATION CLASS MAGIC,
WHICH CAN ALTER THE COURSE OF
TWO OR 3 BATTLES AT A TIME.
TACTICAL GOES ONE STEP FURTHER.
A CASTER OF A
TACTICAL CLASS SPELL
COULD CONCEIVABLY CONQUER A
STRUCTURE AS LARGE AS A CASTLE.
DOES THAT MEAN HE COULD ALSO
DESTROY AN ENTIRE DUNGEON?
[SHIROE, THINKING] THE GAME
DOESN'T HAVE SPELLS LIKE THAT.
AND I DON'T, EITHER.
STRATEGIC CLASS WOULD
BE A SINGLE SPELL
THAT COULD DECIDE
THE OUTCOME OF A WAR.
AND NATIONAL DEFENSE,
AN ENTIRE NATION.
AND OF COURSE,
CONTINENT CLASS, A CONTINENT.
AND THUS, WORLD CLASS.
[SHIROE] OK. A SPELL CAPABLE
OF CONTROLLING THE LAWS,
OR THE FATES, OR THE VERY
EXISTENCE OF AN ENTIRE WORLD.
[REGAN] EXACTLY,
MY FRIEND.
[AKATSUKI] UHH.
[SHIROE] MM...
[SHIROE] I UNDERSTAND
THE CONCEPT BEHIND
SPELLS THAT POWERFUL,
BUT HAS ANYONE EVER
ACTUALLY CAST ONE?
[REGAN] HMM. TO THE BEST OF MY
KNOWLEDGE, THERE IS ONE SPELL.
IT'S BEEN CAST 3 TIMES.
IT'S CALLED "THE WORLD
FRACTION GLOBAL ENCHANTMENT."
[SHIROE] OH.
THE APOCALYPSE.
[AKATSUKI] UHH.
[REGAN] HMM. I INVITED YOU HERE
BECAUSE I BELIEVE THAT YOU,
OF ALL THE ADVENTURERS
WHO HAVE BEEN STUCK HERE,
MIGHT ACTUALLY HAVE
INSIGHT INTO THE MATTER.
[SHIROE] OF COURSE. BUT I
HAVE QUESTIONS FOR YOU, TOO.
TO PUT IT MILDLY, WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT LED TO US BEING HERE.
AND WE WOULD REALLY
LIKE TO FIND OUT.
[REGAN] I'D BE HAPPY TO TELL YOU
ANYTHING I KNOW, OF COURSE.
[SHIROE] THEN I'LL
START WITH THIS.
THE FRACTION SPELL.
I GUESS THE BEST THING TO KNOW
ABOUT IT WOULD BE,
WHAT HAPPENED WITH
THE OTHER TWO USES?
THAT IS QUITE A LONG STORY.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT WITH YOU?
[SHIROE] DEFINITELY.
[REGAN] WELL, THEN, AS THEY SAY,
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
[MINORI, THINKING]
FORMATION, OPERATOR,
FIELD MONITOR, PATROL TEAMS.
OK. I REMEMBER EVERYTHING
SHIROE TAUGHT ME ABOUT
FIGHTING IN A PARTY.
BUT WHY AM I SO NERVOUS?
I FEEL LIKE I MUST BE
MISSING SOMETHING.
[REGAN] APPROXIMATELY
350 YEARS AGO,
THE WORLD IS SAID TO HAVE
BEEN A FAR MORE PROSPEROUS
PLACE THAN TODAY.
(PLANES SOARING)
IT'S A PALE SHADOW
OF THE AGE OF GODS,
WHICH HAS PASSED INTO LEGEND.
BUT DURING THAT TIME, HUMANS,
ELVES, DWARVES, AND ALVS...
THESE 4 RACES LIVED TOGETHER.
THE ALVS IN PARTICULAR
WERE MAGICAL INVENTORS
AND THE VANGUARD OF A
VAST MAGICAL CIVILIZATION.
SADLY, HOWEVER, THAT POWER
BECAME THEIR UNDOING.
[AKATSUKI] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
AS A RACE, THEIR REPRODUCTIVE
CAPACITY WAS QUITE SLIM,
AND THEIR NATION WAS SMALL.
THEY WERE DESPISED FOR
THEIR MONOPOLY OVER
MAGICAL TECHNOLOGY,
SO THE OTHER RACES USED
THEIR SUPERIOR NUMBERS
TO ERADICATE THEM.
THEN WHAT ABOUT ME?
MY RACE IS
TECHNICALLY HALF‐ALV.
[REGAN] IN THE PERIOD
THAT FOLLOWED,
THE FEW SURVIVING ALVS
WERE KEPT AS SLAVES.
THEIR DESCENDANTS
ARE THE HALF‐ALVS.
IN ANY EVENT, THE ALV
KINGDOM WAS DESTROYED.
AND THEN THE 6 BENT PRINCESSES,
THE LUQUENJE, WERE BORN.
[AKATSUKI] "6 BENT PRINCESSES"?
[SHIROE] "LUQUENJE"?
[REGAN] EACH OF THE 6 WERE
UNAWARE OF THE OTHER 5,
SO THEY WERE NOT ACTING
TOGETHER AT ALL.
HOWEVER, DRIVEN BY ANGER
OVER THE DESTRUCTION OF
THEIR RACE AND THEIR CULTURE,
ALL OF THESE ALV
WOMEN SOUGHT REVENGE,
UNINTENTIONALLY
AT THE SAME TIME.
SOME OF THEM SEDUCED
MEN OF GREAT POWER.
SOME LED THE REMAINING ALVS
IN IMPROVISED ARMIES.
(EXPLOSION)
AND THE WORLD WAS PLUNGED
INTO A BUBBLING CAULDRON
OF CHAOS ONCE MORE.
BUT IN THE END,
ALL 6 OF THE PRINCESSES
WERE LEFT ON THE
VERGE OF DEFEAT,
AND ALL SEEMED LOST.
AND THAT WAS WHEN
THEY DECIDED TO CAST
THE FIRST WORLD FRACTION SPELL.
AND SO THE PEOPLE WHO
DECIDED TO CAST IT WERE ALVS?
[REGAN] PRECISELY.
BUT THE TECHNOLOGIES
AND PRINCIPLES USED REMAIN
DEEPLY SHROUDED IN MYSTERY.
AND THE SPELL BROUGHT
ABOUT THE GENESIS
OF THE DEMI‐HUMANS.
(SHIROE GASPS)
[REGAN] UNTIL 300 YEARS AGO,
THERE WERE NO DEMI‐HUMANS.
AS TO HOW THEY WERE CREATED,
REPEATED WAR HAD DECREASED
THE POPULATION...
LEAVING THE PLANET
OVERRUN WITH SOULS.
IT IS MY BELIEF THAT
THOSE SURPLUS SOULS
WERE UTILIZED IN THE
CREATION OF THE DEMI‐HUMANS.
THE WARS WITH THE DEMI‐HUMANS
PUSHED HUMANITY TO THE BRINK,
AND THE WORLD SANK
INTO A DARK AGE.
HUMANITY DEFEATED
THE LUQUENJE, OF COURSE,
BUT THE PRINCESSES'
PLANS FOR REVENGE
HAD ULTIMATELY BEEN
PROVEN SUCCESSFUL.
[SHIROE] HMM.
HUMANITY, FACED WITH AN
OVERRUN OF DEMI‐HUMAN RACES,
USED ALV MAGICAL SECRETS TO
ADD ALLIES TO THEIR NUMBERS.
AND SO THE CAT
PEOPLE, WOLF FANGS,
FOX TAILS, AND ROBED ONES
JOINED THE RANKS OF HUMANITY
TO FIGHT DEMI‐HUMANS.
THIS ALSO COINCIDED WITH THE
CREATION OF THE PRECURSORS.
[SHIROE] THE PRECURSORS
ARE AMONG THE MOST
POWERFUL NON‐PLAYER CHARACTERS,
WITH STRENGTH RIVALING
THAT OF ADVENTURERS.
AS YOU KNOW FROM
THE STORY OF THE GAME,
PRECURSORS ARE CONSIDERED
TO BE LEGENDARY HEROES.
[REGAN] WE CAN DISCUSS
THE PRECURSORS AT ANOTHER
TIME, OF COURSE.
THE ISSUE NOW AT HAND
SEEMS TO BE SOULS.
IN MAGICAL SCIENCE TERMS,
WE REFER TO THIS AS
SPIRITUAL THEORY.
[SHIROE] "SPIRITUAL THEORY"?
[REGAN] AND IN SPITE OF
USING THE PROCESS
TO CREATE ALLIES
OF THEIR OWN,
HUMANITY COULDN'T
STOP THE ONSLAUGHT.
SO, NO MATTER HOW MANY
DEMI‐HUMANS ONE DEFEATED,
THEY WERE ALWAYS
REINCARNATING.
WHICH MEANS THEY CAN
NEVER REALLY BE DEFEATED.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
IS HE TALKING ABOUT RESPAWNS?
I THOUGHT THAT WAS
PART OF THE GAME.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] SAY YOU
KILL EVERY MONSTER IN A ZONE,
THERE'D BE NOTHING LEFT FOR
OTHER PLAYERS WITHOUT RESPAWNS.
NO FIGHTS, NO EXPERIENCE POINTS,
NO LEVELING UP.
HOWEVER, A TIMER IN THE
GAME ALWAYS MAKES SURE
THE ZONE IS REPOPULATED
FOR A FIGHT,
AND THAT'S RESPAWNING.
[REGAN] THE CONSTANT BATTLES
WITH THE DEMI‐HUMANS RAGED ON.
BUT 60 YEARS AFTER THE
FIRST WORLD FRACTION,
HUMANITY WAS NEARLY ANNIHILATED.
AND THEN, A DIVINE
SUMMONING SPELL WAS USED,
AND MESSENGERS OF GOD MADE
THEIR WAY TO THIS WORLD.
THIS WAS 240 YEARS AGO.
THE SECOND WORLD FRACTION.
WHICH HERALDED THE APPEARANCE
OF THE ADVENTURERS.
[SHIROE] 240 YEARS AGO.
SO TELL ME, WHY DID YOU
WANT TO TALK TO ME
ABOUT ALL THIS
IN THE FIRST PLACE?
[REGAN] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[SHIROE] THERE ARE OTHER
ROUND TABLE REPRESENTATIVES.
THERE ARE OTHER REPRESENTATIVES,
BUT YOU'RE A MASTER MAGE.
YOU MIGHT HAVE A BETTER
UNDERSTANDING OF THIS
THAN THEY DO.
UHH! WAIT, AN ARCH‐MAGE?
IS THAT REALLY TRUE, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] I DON'T KNOW.
OUR HISTORY BOOKS
STARTED DETAILING
THE DEEDS OF THE MASTER
MAGE SHIROE 98 YEARS AGO.
IN FACT, THE TIME
YOU'VE BEEN ACTIVE ALONE
IS PROOF THAT YOU'RE A
MASTER MAGE IN THIS WORLD.
98 YEARS AGO?
I KNOW YOU CAN'T BE
THAT OLD, MY LORD.
[SHIROE]
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
[SHIROE, THINKING] WAIT!
I JUST REMEMBERED...
5 MINUTES OF PLAYING TIME
IS EQUAL TO AN HOUR
ON THE GAME TIMER.
IN OTHER WORDS,
ONE DAY IN THE GAME
EQUALS TWO REAL‐WORLD HOURS.
SO 98 OF THEIR YEARS
IS A LITTLE MORE THAN
8 YEARS FOR US.
SO WHAT WAS I DOING
8 YEARS AND 3 MONTHS AGO?
OF COURSE. THAT'S WHEN
I STARTED PLAYING ELDER TALES.
(GASP)
ADVENTURERS FIRST APPEARED IN
THEIR WORLD 240 YEARS AGO,
OR 20 YEARS AGO FOR US.
THAT MAKES SENSE, TOO.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHEN THEY
STARTED THE OPEN BETA TEST
FOR THE GAME ONLINE.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
[TAKAYAMA] HONESTLY,
I WAS EXPECTING MORE NOBLES
TO ASK US FOR TROOPS.
[KRUSTY] YES. MOST OF THEM
WANT TECHNOLOGY SHARING
OR TRADE AGREEMENTS.
[MICHITAKA] THEY KNEW ALL
ABOUT THE STEAM ENGINE.
[TAKAYAMA] AND WE KNOW
THEY HAD SPIES CRAWLING ALL
OVER THE PLACE IN AKIHABARA.
[SHIROE] KNOWING ABOUT IT
DOESN'T MEAN THEY'D BE ABLE
TO MAKE ONE THAT EASILY.
[KRUSTY] SHIROE'S RIGHT.
THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT NOW.
[MICHITAKA] WHAT ABOUT
A FEW YEARS FROM NOW?
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD.
[SHIROE] HM?
THINKING ABOUT
YESTERDAY?
I AM.
[SHIROE] WHAT IS THIS SPIRITUAL
THEORY YOU MENTIONED?
THE ENERGY THAT ANIMATES
ALL LIVING THINGS IS COMMONLY
REFERRED TO AS THE SPIRIT.
AND SPIRIT ITSELF CAN BE
DIVIDED INTO TWO COMPONENTS...
THE PSYCHE AND THE ANIMA.
PSYCHE IS THE ENERGY
THAT ANIMATES THE MIND,
AND IT AFFECTS THINGS
SUCH AS MAGIC AS WELL.
YOU CALL IT MP,
OR MAGIC POINTS.
ANIMA IS THE ENERGY
THAT ANIMATES THE BODY.
YOU CALL THEM
HIT POINTS, OR HEALTH.
IT IS ALSO KNOWN AS KI, OR CHI.
WHEN SOMEONE IS
DEFEATED IN BATTLE,
THEY CAN NO LONGER MOVE,
BUT THE MIND STILL
REMAINS HEALTHY.
[SMASH] UHH.
[REGAN] HOWEVER, THE ANIMA
AND PSYCHE ARE SPLIT,
AND THE PSYCHE BECOMES
TRAPPED IN DARKNESS AS
THE BODY ITSELF FAILS.
THIS IS BECAUSE THE
INFORMATION THAT FLOWS
TO THE MIND FROM THE BODY,
WHICH SENSES LIGHT,
HAS BEEN CUT OFF.
THEN THE DISPERSAL OF
THE BODY, THE ANIMA, BEGINS.
THIS PROCESS IS CALLED
ANIMA‐DISPERSAL.
RESURRECTION MAGIC CAN BE USED
ON CORPSES IN THIS STATE.
THE PROCESS GATHERS
AND RECONSTRUCTS THE ANIMA
THAT HAS OTHERWISE DISPERSED
AFTER A PHYSICAL DEATH.
THE INFORMATION REQUIRED FOR THE
RECONSTRUCTION IS DERIVED BY
CALCULATING BACKWARDS FROM THE
INFORMATION LEFT IN THE CORPSE.
WITH THE CORPSE CONTAINING
ITS OWN BLUEPRINT,
THE HEALER SIMPLY PROVIDES
THE ENERGY TO EFFECT
THE RESURRECTION.
[SHIROE] HOWEVER,
PIECES ARE ALWAYS MISSING,
SO ANY RESTORATION IS
AN IMPERFECT TASK AT BEST.
AND THAT'S WHY YOU LOSE
EXPERIENCE AFTER RESURRECTION.
[REGAN] BECAUSE DECAY
STARTS IMMEDIATELY,
YOU'LL ALWAYS LOSE SOMETHING.
NATURALLY, IF THE BODY,
THE ANIMA, DISPERSES COMPLETELY,
RESURRECTION BECOMES IMPOSSIBLE.
AND OF COURSE, PEOPLE OF THE
LAND PERISH AT THIS POINT.
OK, BUT WHAT
ABOUT BEFORE THEN?
[REGAN] RESURRECTION MAGIC WILL
WORK ON PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
FOR AN ADVENTURER, THOUGH,
ONCE HIS ANIMA IS DISPERSED,
HIS BODY DECOMPOSES
INTO PARTICLES AND
THE PSYCHE, THE MIND,
USES ITS POWER TO
TRANSPORT THE ADVENTURER
TO THE CATHEDRAL.
YOU ARE AWARE OF THIS, I'M SURE.
THIS SYSTEM IS QUITE SIMILAR
TO THAT OF THE DEMI‐HUMANS
AND THEIR RESPAWNS.
OF COURSE, THIS IS NOTHING
MORE THAN A HYPOTHESIS
THAT MY MASTER AND I WERE
RESEARCHING QUITE A WHILE AGO.
[SHIROE] DID YOU CONSIDER
THE POSSIBILITY
THAT DEMI‐HUMANS HAD
MEMORIES BEFORE THEY DIED?
[REGAN] ACTUALLY, NO.
AN INDIVIDUAL'S PERSONALITY
AND CONSCIOUSNESS
ARE STORED INSIDE THE
PSYCHE AS INFORMATION.
MEMORIES, HOWEVER, ARE ALSO
STORED WITHIN THE BRAIN.
THE BODY, OF COURSE,
BEING ANIMA.
[SHIROE] SO YOU'RE
SAYING MEMORIES EXIST
BOTH WITHIN THE ANIMA
AND THE PSYCHE.
WOULDN'T THAT MEAN THAT
MEMORIES COULD BE LOST EVERY
TIME SOMEONE REINCARNATES?
[REGAN] OH. NOW THAT
YOU MENTION IT.
I DON'T SEE HOW SOMEONE
COULD GO THROUGH
SOMETHING THAT TRAUMATIC AND
NOT LOSE A MEMORY OR TWO.
(SHIROE SIGHS)
[REGAN] THE FIRST
WORLD FRACTION CURSE
USED EXISTING SOULS TO
MAKE UNREASONING FIGHTING
MONSTERS OUT OF THEM.
THEIR OLD MEMORIES MAY BE THERE,
BUT THE MONSTERS THEY'VE
BECOME WOULD HAVE NO WAY
TO RECOGNIZE THEM.
[REGAN] THE MEMORIES OF WHAT
THEY ONCE WERE MIGHT BE LIKE
A DREAM OR A STORY.
[SHIROE, THINKING] DOES THAT
MEAN WE COULD WIND UP LOSING
OUR MEMORIES AS WELL?
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD.
[SHIROE] UHH.
[AKATSUKI] MM.
[SHIROE] UH, HEH, HEH.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS.
[SHIROE] HUH.
[AKATSUKI] IF WE DIE
IN THIS WORLD,
DON'T WE SIMPLY REVIVE
AT THE CATHEDRAL?
THE PERSON SITTING AT
THE COMPUTER PLAYING THE
ELDER TALES GAME IS THE MIND.
IN OTHER WORDS, THE PSYCHE.
THE CHARACTER INSIDE THE SCREEN
IS THE BODY, THE ANIMA.
NATURALLY, THE PLAYER IS THE
ONE WITH THE MEMORIES OF WHAT
HAPPENED DURING THE GAME,
BUT THE PLAYER'S CHARACTER IS
THE ONE WITH THE EXPERIENCE,
THE ITEMS, THE LEVELS,
AND OTHER TYPES OF POINTS.
UNTIL NOW, IF A CHARACTER DIED,
IT ONLY MEANT LOSING
EXPERIENCE IN THE GAME.
[IN‐GAME SHIROE] UHH.
[SHIROE] THE REAL‐WORLD
DISCONNECT
MEANT IT DIDN'T HURT US.
HOWEVER, NOW OUR PSYCHE
AND ANIMA, THEY'RE
IN THE SAME PLACE,
SO WE DON'T GET THAT SAME
PROTECTION WE USED TO HAVE.
[AKATSUKI] SO WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING IS...
[SHIROE] IT MEANS OUR MEMORIES
AND OUR EXPERIENCE POINTS
ARE NOW THE SAME,
BUT IRREPLACEABLE.
IF WE DIE, WE'LL LOSE
OUR MEMORIES...
LIKE OUR EXPERIENCE.
UHH!
[SHIROE] BUT I HAVE NO
IDEA HOW MUCH WE'D LOSE.
SINCE WE CAME TO THIS WORLD,
MANY PEOPLE HAVE DIED,
BUT NONE OF THEM
HAVE COMPLAINED,
SO IT MAY BE NOTHING.
IT MAY BE NO MORE THAN
JUST A LITTLE FORGETFULNESS.
[AKATSUKI] YEAH, BUT EVEN SO...
[SHIROE] OR MAYBE YOU FORGET
AND YOU DON'T REALIZE YOU DID.
JUST THINK IF YOU FORGOT
ABOUT THE REAL WORLD.
ANYWAY, IT'S PROBABLY BEST IF
WE SIT ON THIS FOR A WHILE.
[SHIROE] OK?
YES.
(ISUZU YAWNS)
GOOD MORNING.
MORNING, ISUZU.
YOU'RE UP EARLY.
I KNOW.
I REALLY COULDN'T
SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
ME, TOO, I GUESS.
I WONDER IF IT'LL
GO WELL TODAY...
[MINORI] MM.
[ISUZU] UHH. MMM‐WAH.
I THINK I'LL GET A BATH
IN WHILE IT'S EARLY!
[MINORI] OH? OK. SEE YA.
(RUSTLING)
HUH?
(TOYA GRUNTING SOFTLY)
[MINORI] TOYA. GOOD MORNING.
[TOYA] MM‐HMM.
[MINORI] HMM.
(THUNDER)
(RUMBLING)
[ISUZU] UH?
(RUDY GRUNTING)
AHH‐AHH!
(PANTING)
HUH?
HOLD ON A SECOND.
[ISUZU, THINKING] THOSE
ARE DUNGEON CORRIDORS.
(RUDY BREATHING HEAVILY)
[ISUZU, THINKING]
HE'S PRACTICING.
HUH?
[ISUZU] OH! UH, SORRY!
WELL, HELLO, MISS ISUZU!
SPLENDID MORNING, MADAME?!
[ISUZU] THAT'S A LITTLE BIT
MUCH, DON'T YOU THINK?
[RUDY] AND WHAT
DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
I WAS JUST TAKING MY
MORNING CONSTITUTIONAL,
INVITED BY THE FOREST
NYMPHS THEMSELVES
TO LISTEN TO THE BIRDS
AND THEIR SYMPHONY.
HEE HEE. UH...
WELL, IF YOU
SAY SO.
I DO.
SO WHAT BRINGS YOU OUT
HERE ON THIS FINE DAY?
THOUGHT I'D GET
A BATH IN.
HEY, I KNOW!
WHY DON'T YOU COME DOWN
TO THE STREAM WITH ME?
[RUDY] TO THE‐
TO THE BATH!
I'M NOT INTERESTED IN
BEING A PEEPING TOM
WHO STARES AT WOMEN
WHO ARE BATHING!
DON'T INSULT ME
LIKE THAT.
[ISUZU] I WASN'T TELLING YOU
TO COME STARE AT ME, YOU DUMMY!
I MEANT YOU WOULDN'T WANT A LADY
TO WALK THROUGH THE FOREST
BY HERSELF AND
GET HURT, WOULD YOU?
OH. I SEE...
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
I GUESS I COULD‐
YES! I'LL GLADLY
ESCORT YOU!
IT WOULD BE MY HONOR, MA'AM.
SO, WHICH WAY IS
THIS SPRING OF YOURS?
(ISUZU GIGGLES)
[ISUZU] THAT WAY, RUNDELLHAUS.
[RUDY] MISS ISUZU, PLEASE.
MY PARENTS CALL ME RUNDELLHAUS.
JUST CALL ME RUDY.
(RAIN FALLING)
MM! DELICIOSO!
ANOTHER WONDERFUL
BREAKFAST TODAY.
DON'T YOU ALL THINK SO?
MY MOUTH IS IN FOOD HEAVEN.
IT'S NYANTA'S
SPECIAL RECIPE!
RUDY, YOU OUGHT
TO GIVE THIS A TRY!
[MINORI] HMM?
WHAT'D YOU CALL HIM?
[RUDY] MM‐MMM!
MASHED PUMPKIN SALAD.
THIS IS TRULY
AN EXQUISITE TASTE.
SO REFINED, SO YUMMY
IN MY TUMMY.
[MINORI] OH.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
G‐G‐G‐G‐I'M SO SORRY!
THERE'S NO MORE SOUP!
I SHOULD'VE THOUGHT ABOUT
GETTING MORE FOR US!
I'M SORRY!
I WASN'T TALKING
ABOUT THAT. HMM.
[MINORI] UH?
[MINORI, THINKING] TOYA'S GOT
THE SAME THING ON HIS MIND I DO.
[TOYA] SO GUYS, I WAS
THINKING, YOU KNOW...
[MINORI, THINKING] WAIT...
I DON'T WANT IT TO END
UP LIKE LAST TIME.
IF I'M TOO SCARED TO SAY IT,
NOTHING WILL CHANGE.
I'VE GOTTA SAY SOMETHING.
[RUDY] ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE DONE HERE.
LET'S GET OUR GEAR TOGETHER
AND HEAD OUT TO THE DUNGEON
AND PRACTICE, YOU GUYS.
TODAY I'LL FINALLY‐
[MINORI] OH, COME ON!
[ALL BUT MINORI] HUH?
[MINORI] LOOK, YOU GUYS.
WE NEED TO DISCUSS
WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO,
OR WE WON'T BE
ABLE TO WIN THIS.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
THE REAL ANSWER ISN'T
WRITTEN DOWN ANYWHERE.
NOT IN A TEXTBOOK,
NOT ON THE INTERNET,
AND NOT IN YOUR NOTEBOOK.
AND NO ONE CAN TEACH
IT TO YOU, EITHER.
BUT WHEN YOU FINALLY
UNDERSTAND IT ON YOUR OWN,
WHAT WAS ONCE MERELY A PARTY
BECOMES A GROUP OF TRUE FRIENDS.
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.