[MAN 1] THE SILVER SWORD
GUYS ARE HERE, TOO?
[MAN 2] LOOK, ANOTHER ONE!
[MAN 3] SERIOUSLY?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] THERE
ARE MANY GUILDS WITH MANY
DIFFERENT GOALS.
THE WARRIOR GUILDS USUALLY
SPEND MOST OF THEIR TIME
TRYING TO GET STRONGER.
IN AKIHABARA,
THE MAJOR ONES ARE D. D. D.,
THE BLACK SWORD KNIGHTS,
HONESTY,
THE BRIGADE OF THE WEST WIND...
[RUSHING WIND]
... AND SILVER SWORD.
THERE ARE ALSO CRAFTING GUILDS,
WHOSE TIME IS PRIMARILY OCCUPIED
BY AMASSING ITEMS OR
SELLING THEM IN TOWN.
MARINE AGENCY.
RODERICK MERCHANT GUILD.
SHOPPING STREET 8.
GLENDALE.
RADIO MARKET.
AND THERE'S THE SUPPORT GUILD,
MARIELLE'S CRESCENT
MOON ALLIANCE...
AND NOW... LOG HORIZON.
[BYSTANDER 1] SO ALL THE
MAJOR GUILD MASTERS ARE
HERE AT THE SAME PLACE
AT THE SAME TIME?
[BYSTANDER 2] I GOT A BAD
FEELING ABOUT THIS.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] IT'S A GOOD
SIGN THAT EVERYONE CAME.
ASKING SOJIRO TO HANDLE
THE INVITATIONS WAS A GOOD CALL.
[SHIROE] THANK YOU ALL FOR
TAKING THE TIME TO COME TODAY.
WELCOME. I'M SHIROE,
GUILD MASTER OF LOG HORIZON.
[ISAAC] WHY DON'T WE
KEEP THE INTRODUCTIONS
SHORT AND SWEET, OK,
FORMER STRATEGIST OF
THE TEA PARTY?
[SHIROE] THANK YOU FOR
YOUR RECOGNITION, ISAAC.
I'M FLATTERED THAT
YOU REMEMBER ME
AFTER ALL THIS TIME.
HOW COULD I FORGET?
[WILLIAM MASSACHUSETTS]
WELL, IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHAT
I'M DOING HERE.
[SHIROE]
YOU ARE ALL HERE BECAUSE
WE BELIEVE YOUR GUILDS HAVE
THE ABILITY TO AFFECT
THE CURRENT STATE OF AFFAIRS
IN THE CITY OF AKIHABARA.
WE HAVE BEEN TRAPPED IN THIS
WORLD EVER SINCE THE EVENT
MOST OF US HAVE REFERRED
TO AS "THE APOCALYPSE."
CURRENTLY, WE DON'T HAVE
A FORESEEABLE WAY
OF RETURNING HOME.
IN CONSIDERATION OF THESE FACTS,
THIS CONFERENCE WAS CALLED
TO KEEP THINGS IN THE CITY
FROM GETTING ANY WORSE.
YOU DON'T ASK FOR
MUCH, DO YOU?
[KRUSTY] OK, SHIROE, ARE WE
TALKING ABOUT ORCHESTRATING
ANOTHER ALLIANCE OF
THE SMALLER GUILDS?
IT'S POSSIBLE.
HOWEVER, IT'S MY
UNDERSTANDING
THAT CONFERENCE
ENDED IN FAILURE.
I THINK WE'RE ALL
AWARE OF THE ISSUES
THAT CAUSED THAT MEETING
TO CAVE IN ON ITSELF.
[AKANEYA] FOREMOST OF WHICH WAS
THE NOTION THAT SMALLER GUILDS
NEEDED TO UNITE IN ORDER TO GET
WHAT THE LARGER GUILDS HAD.
AND THE DISCUSSION
TURNED INTO,
"THIS GUILD WANTS THIS" AND,
"THAT GUILD NEEDS THAT."
SO THERE REALLY WASN'T ANY
UNDERLYING UNIFICATION AT ALL.
SO IF I'M UNDERSTANDING
THIS CORRECTLY,
THE PURPOSE OF THIS
CONFERENCE IS TO PREVENT
OUR FUTURE INTERESTS FROM
CONFLICTING WITH EACH OTHER?
RIGHT. THAT'S NOT VERY
LIKELY, IS IT, NOW?
[NYAN‐TA]
EVERYONE SEEMS TO BE
ASSUMING THAT THIS WOULD BE
A CONTINUATION OF THE FIRST
FAILED GUILD ALLIANCE.
[HENRIETTA] CORRECTING THEM
QUICKLY WOULD PROBABLY BE
THE BEST COURSE OF ACTION.
[SHIROE] THAT'S NOT OUR
INTENTION THIS TIME.
MY GOAL IS ULTIMATELY
TO IMPROVE LIFE
HERE IN AKIHABARA.
THAT'S ALL.
ALL RIGHT. YOU GO AHEAD
AND DISCUSS THAT.
SILVER SWORD IS A
FIGHTING ORGANIZATION.
AND WE HAVE NO INTEREST
IN PETTY POLITICS.
WE'LL STILL COME BY
TO SELL OUR WINNINGS TO
THE MERCHANTS, OF COURSE.
JUST DO US A FAVOR...
DON'T ASK US TO COME
IN HERE AND FIX THE
CITY FOR YOU AGAIN.
[MARIELLE] HM...
[MASSACHUSETTS] YOU WANT TO LIVE
HERE AND TRY TO DEAL WITH ALL
ITS LITTLE ISSUES,
THEN FEEL FREE.
IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF
CHARMING THAT YOU THINK
YOU CAN TALK IT ALL OUT.
BUT I KNOW A WASTE OF
TIME WHEN I SEE ONE.
[MASSACHUSETTS]
REGARDLESS, WE'RE
NOT INTERESTED.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DO IT WITHOUT US.
[DOOR CLOSES]
IT LOOKS LIKE
SILVER SWORD IS OUT.
[NYAN‐TA]
YEAH, WE EXPECTED AS
MUCH FROM THAT FOOL.
WELL, UH, IT'S SUCH AN
IMPORTANT DAY FOR EVERYONE.
BUT I DON'T SEE A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT WE KNOW HERE.
I HAVEN'T SEEN
AKATSUKI OR NAOTSUGU
OR EVEN SHORYU OR HIEN.
WHERE ARE THEY?
[HENRIETTA] COME
TO THINK OF IT...
[NYAN‐TA]
I'M SURE THEY'RE
JUST PREOCCUPIED.
[ISUZU] SO ARE THE
RUMORS REALLY TRUE,
THAT WE CAN MAKE
AN ESCAPE OUT
OF THIS PLACE?
YEAH, I GOT WORD
THIS MORNING.
[SHIROE] AS SOON
AS TOYA AND HAMELIN'S
HUNTING PARTY LEAVE,
FOLLOW THEM OUT
OF YOUR GUILD HALL.
GET ALL YOUR NEW
PLAYERS TO FOLLOW.
ALL YOU NEED TO DO IS
WALK OUT THE DOOR.
A FEMALE ASSASSIN
NAMED AKATSUKI
WILL BE IN THE MAIN HALLWAY.
HER BACKUP, AND YOURS,
IS A LEVEL 90 GUARDIAN
WHO'S WATCHING
THE CATHEDRAL. NAOTSUGU.
I WISH I COULD BE THERE.
DON'T WORRY.
THE ENTIRE GUILD BUILDING
IS UNDER MY CONTROL.
(ONE COUGH)
HE SAID ALL WE NEED TO DO TO
ESCAPE IS TO GET OUT THE DOOR.
SO LET'S JUST RUN
LIKE CRAZY, OK?
[YOUNG PLAYERS]
ALL RIGHT! YOU GOT IT!
OK, BUT WHAT DID HE MEAN BY
"THE GUILD BUILDING WAS
UNDER HIS CONTROL"?
I DON'T KNOW. BUT HE
SAID ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS RUN OUT THE DOOR.
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT] HEY!
[BOTH] HUH?
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT]
WHAT ARE YOU RUNNING
YOUR MOUTH ABOUT?
[MINORI] UH, NOTHING, SIR.
[ISUZU] UH, NOTHING.
[SHIROE]
CONTINUING ON...
I'VE CALLED THIS MEETING TO
CREATE A COUNCIL TO DISCUSS
AND POSSIBLY RESOLVE THE
SOCIAL ISSUES IN THIS CITY,
A "ROUND TABLE"
CONFERENCE,
IF YOU WILL.
OUR IMMEDIATE GOAL SHOULD
BE TO IMPROVE THE CITY'S
ATMOSPHERE AND SAFETY.
AFTER THAT, WE SHOULD
RECONVENE WHEN IT'S NECESSARY
TO DISCUSS ISSUES
AS THEY ARISE.
[SERARA] HMM...
[HENRIETTA] THIS IS THE PART
WHERE IT STARTS GETTING SERIOUS.
[KRUSTY]
BEFORE WE GET TO THAT,
WHY DID YOU SPECIFICALLY
INVITE WHO YOU DID TODAY?
[SHIROE]
OF COURSE.
FIRST, WARRIOR GUILDS.
BLACK SWORD KNIGHTS,
HONESTY,
D. D. D.,
THE WEST WIND BRIGADE.
YOU'RE THE STRONGEST
AND HAVE INVESTED
QUITE A BIT OF TIME AND
TALENT IN THE CITY ALREADY.
SILVER SWORD HAS CHOSEN
TO DISREGARD THIS.
MARINE AGENCY,
RODERICK MERCHANT GUILD,
AND SHOPPING STREET 8
WERE CHOSEN TO REPRESENT
THE CRAFTING GUILDS.
CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE,
GLENDALE, AND RADIO MARKET
AREN'T JUST HERE
OF THEIR OWN ACCORD.
THEIR VOICE IS THE
VOICE OF ADVENTURERS
IN SMALLER GUILDS
AND THOSE WHO
HAVEN'T JOINED ONE.
IT'S THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
[EINS]
AND QUITE NECESSARY.
COMBINED, THE GUILDS
ONLY REPRESENT AROUND
6,000 PLAYERS IN THE CITY.
HMM, AND THAT MEANS
TECHNICALLY 9,000 PLAYERS
IN THE CITY DON'T HAVE
A VOICE AT THIS TABLE.
BUT WITH THE SMALLER
GUILDS HERE,
THEY CAN HAVE AT LEAST
A VOICE BY PROXY.
[KRUSTY] AND YOU?
[SHIROE] I'M HERE AS ORGANIZER
OF THIS CONFERENCE
AND AUTHOR OF ITS PROPOSALS.
LOG HORIZON ONLY
HAS 4 MEMBERS,
AT LEAST FOR NOW.
OTHERWISE THEY WOULDN'T HAVE
THE RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE
AT A POLITICAL CONFERENCE
SUCH AS THIS, HMM.
SO BASICALLY, YOU
ORGANIZED THIS MEETING
AND INVITED EVERYONE HERE
KNOWING FULL WELL IT WAS
YOUR ONLY CHANCE TO HAVE
ANY SORT OF INPUT.
[SHIROE]
THAT'S CORRECT.
LET'S SAY FOR NOW WE CREATE
THIS LITTLE COUNCIL OF YOURS.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO KEEP THE PEACE?
AND JUST WHERE DO YOU GET OFF
SAYING THAT THE CITY ISN'T SAFE
AND WE GOT TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT?
[SHIROE]
HM... ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TELL YOU.
THIS SHOULDN'T BE
NEWS TO ANYONE,
HOWEVER, THERE IS A TREND
IN PROTECTION
RACKETEERING GOING ON.
[ISAAC] HUH?!
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT
THE EXP POTIONS.
[SHRADER] LISTEN UP.
IT'S TIME TO GO HUNTING.
GET YOUR GEAR AND MEET
ME OUTSIDE LIKE USUAL.
CRAFTERS, MAKE SURE YOU
REACH YOUR QUOTAS THIS TIME.
YOU HEAR ME?
[CHIME]
[TOYA] BROTHER SHIROE,
WE'RE READY. ARE YOU?
(SHIROE COUGHS)
[TOYA]
ONE COUGH. ALL RIGHT.
IT'S TIME TO GET OUT
OF HERE, EVERYBODY.
[ISAAC] OK, TEA PARTY BOY,
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT'S ILLEGAL ABOUT IT?
[SHIROE] TO THE BEST
OF OUR UNDERSTANDING,
THERE IS NO RULE OF LAW.
SURE THERE IS.
EVERY CITY HAS THE
NO COMBAT ZONES.
[SHIROE] THE ROYAL GUARD IS
A REFLEX OF THE GAMING SOFTWARE.
YOU FIGHT IN THE CITY, YOU DIE.
IT'S NOT NECESSARILY A LAW
BUT SOMETHING TO BE
TREATED ALMOST
AS SOME SORT OF
NATURAL PHENOMENON.
[MARIELLE]
TOTALLY. LAWS ARE WHAT PEOPLE
CREATE AND OTHERS RECOGNIZE.
AT LEAST THAT'S WHAT
HENRIETTA TOLD ME!
HUH?
I LED A PARTY TO
SUSUKINO A FEW DAYS AGO.
TO SUSUKINO?
[SHIROE] THE DOMINANT
GUILD THERE HAD THE
CITY IN A STRANGLEHOLD
OF BULLYING AND DOMINATION
DIRECTED AT BOTH
ADVENTURERS AND NPCs.
WE RISKED A LOT TO BRING
ONE OF OUR FRIENDS HOME.
WE HAD TO GO FIGHT THEM.
BUT THE ROYAL GUARD
DID NOTHING.
[SERARA] UH!
[SHIROE] SO NO ONE IN THAT
BATTLE DID ANYTHING ILLEGAL,
THEM OR US.
BUT WAS IS RIGHT?
IS THAT HOW THINGS SHOULD BE?
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE IS TRYING TO
EXPLAIN TO EVERYONE THAT WE NEED
SOME FORM OF RULES
AND REGULATIONS
IN ORDER TO BIND US TOGETHER
IN THIS LAWLESS WORLD.
[NYAN‐TA] WE APPEAR TO HAVE
A STALEMATE, MY FRIENDS.
SOME OF US ARE DESPERATE TO HAVE
SOME RULE OF LAW IN PLACE,
AND OTHERS STILL THINK THIS IS
A GAME THAT WE SHOULD KEEP DOING
AS WE PLEASE, HMM.
[KRUSTY]
REITERATING ISAAC'S POINT,
AND I'M LOATH TO,
HOW DO WE ENFORCE
OUR DECISIONS AS LAW?
THIS IS GONNA BE
A STICKY SITUATION
WHERE THE LARGER GUILDS
ARE CONCERNED.
[SHIROE] IMPOSE A PENALTY.
[KRUSTY] PENALTY? WHAT KIND?
[SHIROE] BANISH THEM
FROM THE CITY, OF COURSE.
[KRUSTY] BANISHMENT?
[SHIROE] AND IF NECESSARY, WE
MAKE THEM BREAK UP THEIR GUILD.
[AKANEYA]
BANISHMENT? WHAT?
[SOJIRO] WE CAN'T IMPOSE
A DEATH PENALTY ON ANYONE
HERE OR ANYTHING.
HMPH. IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE
GONNA BE ABLE TO ENFORCE
THESE NEW LAWS OF YOURS WITH
YOUR PUNY, LITTLE GUILDS.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED
NUMBERS AND MUSCLE.
BECAUSE WHETHER YOU
LIKE IT OR NOT,
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
THAT MORE THAN A FEW
OF THE MAJOR GUILDS
ARE GONNA LOOK
AT THIS LITTLE LAW
MAKING EFFORT AND SAY,
"SCREW ALL OF YOU!"
AND THEN IT'LL BE WAR.
IF ONE OF THE MAJOR GUILDS
WENT ROGUE ON US,
NONE OF US WOULD BE IN
A POSITION TO STOP
THEM FROM DOING IT.
[KRUSTY] SHIROE, I DON'T
REALLY THINK THAT YOU'VE
THOUGHT THIS ALL THE WAY
THROUGH LIKE YOU USUALLY DO.
I TRULY BELIEVE PUTTING TOGETHER
THE ROUND TABLE IS A GOOD IDEA.
BUT IN THE END, ISN'T IT REALLY
JUST GOING TO BE FOR SHOW?
WE REALLY DON'T WANT THIS
SITUATION TO DEVOLVE INTO‐
[ROBES RUSTLE NOISILY]
HUH?
EARLIER, APPROXIMATELY
4 HOURS AGO THIS MORNING,
THINGS CHANGED.
I BECAME THE SOLE OWNER
AND ADMINISTRATOR
OF THE GUILD BUILDING ZONE.
[EINS] WHAT?
[KARASHIN] HUH?
(ISAAC GASPS)
WHAT DID YOU
JUST SAY?!
THAT WAS COOL.
[SHIROE] NOW, OF COURSE,
I HAVE COMPLETE CONTROL
OVER ACCESS TO THE ZONE.
ACCESS CONTROL MEANS I
SAY WHO COMES AND GOES.
SHORT AND SWEET, I PUT
YOU ON THE BLACK LIST,
YOU'RE NOT GETTING IN...
HUH?
...TO ANYTHING IN
THE GUILD BUILDING.
AND WHEN I SAY ANYTHING,
I MEAN EVERYTHING.
[HENRIETTA] WELL, WELL, WELL.
SHIROE TRULY IS A VILLAIN.
[NYAN‐TA] MMMYEAH.
[SERARA] WHAT DOES HIS BUYING
THE GUILD BUILDING MEAN?
I MEAN, WHAT DID
HE GET OUT OF IT?
[NYAN‐TA] THE GUILD BUILDING
ZONE IS NOW MASTER SHIROE'S
PRIVATE PROPERTY, YOU DIG?
[SERARA] AND WHY IS THAT GONNA
BE A PROBLEM FOR EVERYONE ELSE?
[HENRIETTA] IT'S SIMPLE.
ANY PERSON THAT SHIROE DOES NOT
WANT ENTERING THE GUILD BUILDING
WILL NOT BE ABLE TO.
BUT THE BIGGEST OF THE
BIG GUILDS USUALLY HAVE
THEIR GUILD HALLS AND
GATHERINGS SOMEWHERE
ELSE, DON'T THEY?
TO CREATE, JOIN, OR LEAVE
A GUILD, YOU HAVE TO COME
TO THE GUILD BUILDING.
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
(SERARA GASP)
AND, LEST WE FORGET,
THE BANK IS HERE.
AFTER ALL, IN A
GAMING ENVIRONMENT,
WHAT'S MORE DANGEROUS
THAN WALKING AROUND
WITH LOOSE CHANGE AND
VALUABLES ALL THE TIME?
THAT'S THE QUICKEST WAY
TO GET ROBBED FOR REAL.
THAT'S WHY THE DEVELOPERS
GAVE US THE BANK,
TO KEEP ALL THAT SAFE.
NOW, OF COURSE, IN ELDER TALES,
THERE ARE BANK BRANCHES
IN EVERY SINGLE TOWN YOU COULD
EVER HOPE TO VISIT, HMM.
[HENRIETTA] BUT WITH
THE TRANSPORT GATES OFFLINE,
TRAVEL TO OTHER CITIES IS
ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE.
IN OTHER WORDS...
(EVIL LAUGHTER IN BACKGROUND)
[NYAN‐TA] MASTER SHIROE
CAN, IN EFFECT,
FREEZE THE ASSETS OF ANY
ADVENTURER BY DENYING THEM
ACCESS TO THEIR ACCOUNT.
HE IS THE MAN.
OH, MY GOSH!
THAT MAKES HIM LOOK LIKE
A REAL‐LIVE BAD GUY!
[HENRIETTA]
OH, MY GOODNESS.
OF ALL THE SNEAKY AND
DASTARDLY THINGS OUT THERE,
SHIROE HAS FOUND A WAY TO
OUTDO THEM ALL, HASN'T HE?
AT LEAST THE DEVIL
LOOKS THE PART.
YOU WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT
SHIROE HAD IT IN HIM.
HIS NICKNAME "THE VILLAIN
BEHIND GLASSES" MIGHT BE
RATHER GENEROUS
IF YOU ASK ME.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
A ZONE'S OWNER HAS
THE RIGHT TO CONTROL
WHO ENTERS AND LEAVES IT.
BUT THEY CAN ALSO
DESIGNATE AREAS TO
ALLOW OR PROHIBIT COMBAT.
AND I'M BETTING THAT
BECAUSE HAMELIN NEEDS
TO CONTROL THEIR RECRUITS,
THEIR GUILD HALL PROBABLY
HAS "COMBAT" TURNED ON.
[MINORI]
COME ON. LET'S GO!
(CLANG)
[MINORI] AH!
[GIRLS] HM?
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT]
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
WERE UP TO SOMETHING.
WHERE ARE THE REST
OF YOU BRATS?!
[MINORI] UH!
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT]
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TRYING TO PULL?
[TOYA, THINKING]
DON'T FORGET WHAT
BROTHER SHIROE TAUGHT YOU.
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT] UH! OOF!
(MILD LIGHTNING BOLT GAGGING)
TOYA!
[TOYA, THINKING]
THE SAMURAI'S SKILLS:
SHRIKE IMPALEMENT
AND LANIUS CAPTURE.
IN COMBINATION, THESE
TEMPORARILY MUTE AN ENEMY,
STOPPING HIM FROM
CASTING SPELLS.
[MINORI] GET TO THE EXIT!
[GIRL 1] RIGHT!
[GIRL 2] OKAY!
[TOYA, THINKING]
LANIUS CAPTURE
LASTS 15 SECONDS...
... AND I'M ALMOST
OUT OF TIME!
[MINORI, VOICE‐OVER]
SHRINE MAIDEN HEALING
ABILITY, DAMAGE INTERCEPTION.
IT CREATES A BARRIER AROUND
YOUR ALLY THAT ABSORBS DAMAGE
UP TO A CERTAIN AMOUNT.
I LEARNED IT FROM SHIROE.
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT]
UGH. YOU LITTLE PUNKS.
GET BACK HERE!
I'LL SEND YOU TO THE
CATHEDRAL A HUNDRED TIMES!
[SHRADER] WHAT'S WITH ALL
THE RUCKUS? WHAT'S GOING ON?!
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT]
THEY'RE GETTING AWAY, SIR.
(PANTING)
[SHRADER]
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
ALMOST THERE.
MY LORD, THE
OPERATION'S UNDER WAY.
HM...
DON'T GET
SMART WITH US.
[EINS] BUT KEEPING US FROM
OUR BANK ACCOUNTS?
[WOODSTOCK W]
THAT'S BLACKMAIL,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
[SHIROE] I WAS ANSWERING
HIS QUESTION.
ANYONE WHO OPPOSES
THE ROUND TABLE WILL LOSE
THE RIGHT TO BANK
HERE IN AKIHABARA.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE
SAYING IT'S BLACKMAIL.
[SHIROE] BUT GOING WITH ISAAC'S
PLAN TO JUST WAGE WAR ISN'T?
KILLING WITHOUT
ACTUAL DEATH?
(ISAAC GROANING)
[EINS] PURCHASING THE GUILD
BUILDING ZONE HAD TO HAVE TAKEN
AN ASTRONOMICAL
AMOUNT OF MONEY.
[WOODSTOCK W] ALL RIGHT,
SO WHERE'D YOU GET
THAT KIND OF CASH?
5 MILLION IN GOLD, BOYS,
COURTESY OF MARINE AGENCY.
[GROUP] HUH?
[RODERICK] SO LET ME GET
THIS STRAIGHT...
IT WAS MY UNDERSTANDING
YOU WANTED ALL THAT MONEY
FOR A MAJOR QUEST.
NO, RODERICK, THIS
WAS NOT A QUEST.
I BROUGHT YOU HERE
SOLELY TO CREATE
THE ROUND TABLE.
[KARASHIN]
YOU'VE GOT TO
BE KIDDING.
(MICHITAKA GROANS)
[KARASHIN] THIS IS IT?
[RODERICK] OH, PLEASE!
SOMETHING THIS SIMPLE
WAS THE SECRET RECIPE
FOR THE CRESCENT BURGER?
[MICHITAKA] WAIT. YOU MEAN
WE PAID YOU 5 MILLION
IN GOLD FOR THIS?
[SHIROE]
HISTORICALLY, PEOPLE HAVE
ALWAYS PAID EXCESSIVE SUMS
FOR INFORMATION THEY
DIDN'T POSSESS.
AND THAT'S WHY
YOU PAID FOR IT.
HM?
HMM...
(CHILDREN PANTING HEAVILY)
[TOYA] WE'RE ALMOST
THERE, MINORI!
(MINORI AND TOYA GROANING)
(SHRADER LAUGHS EVILLY)
[SHRADER] AFRAID YOU
FOUND A DEAD END, KIDS.
AH, TOO BAD.
(TOYA AND MINORI GROANING)
[MINORI] TOYA!
[MINORI] YOU CAN'T TAKE
ANY MORE DAMAGE!
PENTAGRAM BARRIER!
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
[MINORI] OH, NO.
[SHRADER] YOU'RE GONNA NEED
MORE POWER THAN THAT!
A LOT MORE!
NIGHTY‐NIGHT, KIDDOS.
[MINORI] TOYA, AAH!
[TOYA] MINORI, NO!
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT] SHRADER!
[SHRADER] YOU'RE LATE. DRAG
THOSE LITTLE BRATS BACK HERE.
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT] RIGHT!
[TOYA] LET'S GO, MINORI!
WE'RE GETTING OUT OF HERE!
(PANTING)
(TOYA YELLING)
[MINORI]
HE'S COMING THROUGH
THAT DOOR, YOU KNOW?!
WHOA... OH, MAN.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT] AAH!
[SHRADER] WHAT'S THE
MATTER WITH YOU?
[MILD LIGHTNING BOLT]
I‐IT WON'T OPEN.
[BUZZING]
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
A CHARACTER WHO OWNS A ZONE
CAN CONTROL WHO
ENTERS AND EXITS.
BY USING AN ACCESS LIST,
THEY CAN KEEP SOMEONE
FROM GETTING IN.
[TOYA] WHAT'S UP?
[MINORI]
NO ONE'S FOLLOWING US.
[SHORYU]
YOU'RE THE LAST, RIGHT?
[MINORI AND TOYA] UH!
I'M SHORYU. SHIROE SENT
ME HERE TO COME GET YOU.
[TOYA] HE DID?
[MINORI] UM, WHERE'S EVERYONE?
[SHORYU] WAITING
AT THE ENTRANCE.
(BOTH GASP)
(CHIME)
HM?
HUH? COME ON. YOU CAN DEAL
WITH THAT, CAN'T YOU?
ANYWAY, LET'S GET YOU
GUYS OUT OF HERE.
[TOYA AND MINORI] RIGHT!
[SHORYU] I TOLD YOU.
YOU STUPID FOX!
THAT'LL CAUSE TROUBLE
FOR MARIELLE...
SORRY.
HEY, QUIT STUMBLING
AROUND, ALREADY.
YOU LOOK KIND OF
PATHETIC, YOU KNOW?
WHATEVER!
YOU'RE SUCH
A MEANIE.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(DOOR BURSTS OPEN)
[SHRADER] COME HERE.
(TOYA YELLS)
(SHRADER GROWLS)
[SHRADER] IT HURTS,
DOESN'T IT, BOY?
BUT THIS DOESN'T COUNT
AS ACTUAL COMBAT.
WHAT HAVE YOU
DONE TO MY HALL,
YOU LITTLE MONSTER?
(TOYA GRUNTS)
[SHRADER] DON'T LOOK
AT ME LIKE THAT, BOY.
(TOYA GRUNTS)
[MINORI] TOYA!
[SHRADER] KEEP IT UP,
AND I'LL BUST YOUR HEAD,
RIGHT HERE AND NOW.
YOU'RE NOT
GOING ANYWHERE.
YOU AND ME,
WE'RE THE SAME.
WE'RE BOTH STUCK HERE
WITH NOWHERE ELSE TO GO.
(SLICING)
(TOYA GRUNTS)
[SHRADER]
WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
[AKATSUKI] I THOUGHT
I HAD MANAGED TO ADD
EVERY ONE OF HAMELIN'S
MEMBERS TO THE BLACK LIST.
[SHRADER] WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
(CHIME)
MY LORD, I'VE
FOUND ANOTHER.
SORRY. THIS ONE
GOT PAST ME.
HIS NAME IS... SHRADER.
KIND OF LIKE SHREDDER, AS IN
HIS FACE JUST LOST A FIGHT
WITH A PAPER SHREDDER.
UH‐HUH.
[SHRADER] YOU'RE BEGGING
FOR SOME PAIN, LITTLE GIRL.
HUH? WHAT THE HELL
JUST HAPPENED?!
(SMACK)
[SHRADER]
OH! MY ARM! MY ARM...
SO, YE OLDE ROYAL
GUARDS WON'T COME
IF I DO THIS
TO YOU, HUH?
I'M REALLY GLAD
YOU SHARED THAT.
WE'LL HAVE TO DO THIS
AGAIN, WAFFLE FACE.
(CRUNCH)
(SHREDDER GROANING)
[NAOTSUGU] WE GOT ONE
OF THEM DOWN AND OUT.
[NAOTSUGU]
GOOD JOB, SQUIRT!
[AKATSUKI]
QUIT CALLING ME THAT,
YOU PILE OF CRAP!
YOU TWO ARE
TOYA AND MINORI?
I AM THE ASSASSIN,
AKATSUKI.
I AM ALSO LORD SHIROE'S
NINJA GUARDSMAN.
[AKATSUKI]
YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS
ARE NOW SAFE.
MY LORD REGRETS NOT BEING HERE,
BUT HE IS FIGHTING ANOTHER
BATTLE AT THE MOMENT.
WHY DON'T WE START BY
GETTING YOU A BATH AND
A COUPLE OF HOT MEALS?
(MINORI CRIES)
[ISAAC] OK. YOU GOT US ALL
EARS NOW. TELL US WHAT YOU WANT.
WE'D LIKE TO HELP OUT,
BUT WE'RE NOT
GONNA AGREE ON MUCH
IF WE HAVE THE THREAT OF
BLACKMAIL HANGING OVER US.
HELP US OUT, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] COME ON, GUYS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
NOBODY HAS A SENSE OF SAFETY
OR SECURITY RIGHT NOW.
DON'T WE HAVE AN OBLIGATION
TO OURSELVES TO KEEP THE PEACE?
I HAVE TWO GOALS FOR
THIS COUNCIL OF OURS.
THE FIRST THING IS TO
CREATE AN ATMOSPHERE
WHERE PEOPLE AREN'T
AFRAID OF SOME BULLY
BREATHING DOWN THEIR
NECK ALL THE TIME.
[WOODSTOCK W] HMM...
[SHIROE] AND ONCE THAT'S DONE,
CREATE LAWS THAT ARE BINDING
ON EVERYONE WHO LIVES HERE,
VISITS HERE, OR TAKES
UP BUSINESS HERE.
DOES ANYONE HAVE AN
ISSUE WITH THAT?
(CHIME)
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD, THE OPERATION
ON HAMELIN WAS A SUCCESS.
HM...
[ISAAC] YOU BETTER START
TAKING THIS SERIOUSLY!
YOU WANT THIS TO
HAPPEN SO BAD? FINE.
THEN THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANT TO KNOW IN RETURN.
YOU AND YOUR GUILD
OBVIOUSLY PUT THIS
THING TOGETHER.
SO LET'S GO OVER
EVERY LITTLE DETAIL
AND WORK IT OUT.
[SHIMMER]
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
SHIROE HAS SUCCEEDED IN
LIBERATING THE NEW PLAYERS.
BUT HIS BATTLE CONTINUES.
HIS GOAL IS TO CREATE A
PLACE WHERE HE BELONGS,
BUT IT WILL BE FOR MORE
THAN HIMSELF ALONE.
HE HAS FRIENDS AND PEOPLE
IN NEED OF PROTECTION.
AND EVERYONE NEEDS A PLACE
WHERE THEY CAN SIT UNDER
THE STARS AND EAT CURRY.
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.