(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
SO, THIS IS AKIHABARA.
IT MIGHT BE A LITTLE
BIT MUCH FOR YOU.
NO, IT'S NOT.
YES, I'M SURE YOU'LL BE
ABLE TO HANDLE IT.
AND I'M SURE THE
NOBLES WOULD AGREE.
[KRUSTY] PRINCESS, I NEED TO
TAKE CARE OF SOME BUSINESS
OVER AT MY GUILD.
MY FRIENDS WILL ACCOMPANY
YOU UNTIL I COME BACK.
[SHIROE] WE HAVEN'T INTRODUCED
OURSELVES YET, HAVE WE?
I AM SHIROE OF
LOG HORIZON.
THIS IS OUR NINJA,
AKATSUKI.
HMM.
IT'S TRULY AN HONOR TO
MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
SO, WHAT SHOULD I DO TO
GET STARTED WITH THIS
PROJECT OF MINE, ANYWAY?
[SHIROE] UH, TO START WITH,
WE NEED TO GET YOU OUT
OF THE STREET, OK?
HUH?
(MICHITAKA GROANS)
THEY LEFT ME IN CHARGE,
BUT THERE REALLY ISN'T ANYTHING
INTERESTING FOR ME TO DO.
I HOPE SHIROE AND THE
PRINCESS ARE HAVING FUN.
A BLACKSMITH ISN'T VERY
GOOD AT DOING NOTHING.
I GOTTA FIND MYSELF
SOMETHING TO FIX.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
HUH?
[WOMAN 1] SIR SOUJIRO,
THIS CUSTARD IS SUPER YUMMY.
[SOUJIRO] UH, THANK YOU.
[WOMAN 2] HEY, MR. MAN,
PAY ATTENTION TO ME, TOO.
[SOUJIRO] UH...
(CHUCKLE)
AWW, POOR SOUJIRO'S
LOOKING SLEEPY.
THEN MAYBE I'LL
SING HIM A LULLABY.
[WOMAN] NO, I WILL!
[WOMAN 2] NO, I WILL.
[NAZUNA] BE CALM. THIS IS
JUST PART OF THE JOB!
DON'T KILL ANYBODY!
(WOMEN TALKING AT ONCE)
[SOUJIRO] LET'S ALL
JUST GET ALONG, OK?
[ALL] AWW!
GOOD GOD ALMIGHTY. I THINK
I'M GONNA FREAKIN' PUKE.
[RAYNESHIA] OH!
(LAUGHTER, CHEERING)
[LYCOPENE] HEY. I WONDER
WHAT EVENT SHE'S GOING TO.
[SMASH] MAYBE IT'S SOME SORT OF
COSPLAY SITUATION GOING ON.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
DOES EVERYONE WALK
THIS FAST AROUND HERE?
OH!
WE HAVE ALL BEEN
ANXIOUSLY AWAITING
THE ARRIVAL OF THE FAMOUS
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
[SHIROE] THANKS.
[KARASHIN] I AM KARASHIN,
THE TRADER.
IT IS NICE TO MEET YOU.
I AM PRINCESS
RAYNESHIA EL‐ARTE COWEN.
THE PLEASURE'S ALL MINE, SIR.
SO, A REAL PRINCESS, HUH?
MORE LOVELY THAN I'D HEARD.
(CLATTERING)
[SHIROE] HMM. I THINK WE NEED
SOMETHING WITH IMPACT.
THE FIRST IMPRESSION
SHOULD BLOW THEM AWAY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
VALKYRIE MAIL?
[KARASHIN] WE DO, AND WE HAVE
ABOUT 7 DIFFERENT STYLES.
BETWEEN MODEL VARIATIONS
AND OUR OWN ORIGINAL DESIGNS,
WE HAVE PLENTY OF OPTIONS.
[SHIROE] THE TOUGH PART'S GOTTA
BE GETTING HER A DECENT WEAPON.
WE GOTTA GET HER
SOMETHING UNDER LEVEL 4.
[ASHLIN] UH, UM?
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[TARO] OH, WOW!
IT'S A REAL PRINCESS!
[LILIANA]
SHE LOOKED RIGHT AT US.
[ASHLIN] SHE'S SO CUTE!
(RAYNESHIA GIGGLES)
[ALL] OH MY GOD, SHE SMILED!
[KARASHIN] THIS IS A
SINGLE‐HANDED WEAPON
WITH HIGH ATTACK POWER.
[SHIROE] WE NEED SOMETHING
FLASHY, BUT NOT TOO FLASHY.
[TARO] PRINCESS, ARE YOU HUNGRY?
[RAYNESHIA] SURE.
UM, I COULD EAT.
[TARO] THEN HERE, HAVE THIS.
YOU EVER EATEN
A CRESCENT BURGER?
OH, MAN. YOU TOTALLY GOT THESE
HERE WITH PERFECT TIMING.
[LILIANA] SHIROE ASKED
ME TO BRING THEM OVER
AS SOON AS THE
PRINCESS GOT HERE.
[ASHLIN] CRESCENT
BURGERS ARE, LIKE,
THE YUMMIEST
EVER, EVER, EVER!
(RAYNESHIA GIGGLES SOFTLY)
[TARO] SHE ATE IT!
[ASHLIN] SHE TOTALLY
EATS LIKE A PRINCESS!
[LILIANA] DO YOU LIKE IT?
CRESCENT BURGERS ARE, LIKE,
OUR FAVORITE
FOOD AROUND HERE.
[RAYNESHIA] OH, YES.
I'VE NEVER HAD ONE BEFORE.
THE FLAVOR IS QUITE‐
[BOY AND GIRLS] OH!
[RAYNESHIA] O‐OH, NO.
[SHIROE] PRINCESS
RAYNESHIA, HERE YOU GO.
[RAYNESHIA] OH!
[SHIROE] CAN YOU HELP HER
WITH THIS, AKATSUKI?
[AKATSUKI] RIGHT.
[LILIANA] WE'LL BE
GLAD TO HELP, TOO.
[SHIROE] ACTUALLY, COULD
YOU GUYS HELP ME OUT
WITH SOMETHING
DIFFERENT INSTEAD?
[BOY AND GIRLS] YES!
I'LL HELP YOU
WITH YOUR DRESS.
UH...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
[RAYNESHIA] THIS
ARMORED OUTFIT...
I THINK IT'S SHOWING OFF
TOO MANY OF MY CURVES.
AND IT'S MAKING SOME OF THEM
EVEN CURVIER, YOU KNOW?
AND, OH, MY GOODNESS,
MY LEGS ARE SHOWING!
[AKATSUKI] YOU'RE TALL,
SO IT HAS TO.
DEAL WITH IT.
[RAYNESHIA] YEAH, OK...
(GASP)
(KARASHIN AND SHIROE GASP)
[SHIROE] LOOKS LIKE WE
HAVE A WINNER, KARASHIN.
[KARASHIN] YES, AND IT'S
ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL ON YOU.
[RAYNESHIA] UH, THANK YOU
FOR SAYING THAT.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
[SMASH] THERE'S A LOT
MORE PEOPLE IN FULL GEAR
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
[LYCOPENE] YEAH, ARE THEY GIVING
OUT A QUEST OR SOMETHING?
(FINGER SNAPS)
(CROWD MURMURING)
[SHIROE] EVERYONE, THANK YOU
FOR MAKING IT OUT HERE EARLY
AND ON SHORT NOTICE, SERIOUSLY.
I'M SHIROE FROM LOG HORIZON.
THE SITUATION AHEAD
OF US IS URGENT,
SO, I WON'T WASTE YOUR TIME.
(RAYNESHIA WHIMPERS)
[SHIROE] WE HAVE
SIGHTED AND ENGAGED
AN ARMY OF UP TO
20,000 GOBLINS
IN THE NORTHERN
KONTO HILLS.
THEIR ADVANCE IS
THREATENING THE LEAGUE
OF FREEDOM CITIES EASTAL.
IF WE STAY HERE, THERE'S
A GOOD CHANCE EASTAL WILL
SURVIVE THE ASSAULT.
HOWEVER, THEY WILL LOSE 30%
OF THEIR ARMIES IN THE BATTLE.
[RAYNESHIA] OH!
(CROWD MURMURING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] EVERYONE
HERE KNOWS BATTLE STRATEGY.
THEY CAN READ MAPS, AND THEY'RE
PLOTTING MOVES ALREADY?
HOW DO THEY KNOW ALL THIS?
THEY'RE REALLY THAT INTELLIGENT?
THE ADVENTURERS HERE,
THEY REALLY ARE MORE
THAN FOOT SOLDIERS.
DOES THAT MEAN THEY
MIGHT EVEN KNOW MORE THAN
OUR MILITARY OFFICERS,
OR THE MEMBERS OF
GRANDFATHER'S COURT?
OK, SO, WHAT DOES
THAT MAKE NOBLES?
WHAT ARE COMMONERS AND SERFS,
FOR THAT MATTER?
OF COURSE, IT'S SAFE TO SAY
DEFENDING AKIHABARA
FROM AN ARMY OF GOBLINS
WOULD NOT BE ALL
THAT DIFFICULT.
AND WE'RE NOT OBLIGATED
TO HELP ANYONE.
WE COULD JUST LET EASTAL
HANDLE IT THEMSELVES.
[RAYNESHIA] UH!
[SHIROE] ULTIMATELY,
WE HAVE NOTHING TO GAIN
BY OFFERING OUR ASSISTANCE.
HOWEVER, THERE'S SOMEONE HERE
WHO I THINK WE SHOULD
LISTEN TO FIRST.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
ALL RIGHT, THEN. YOU'RE UP.
UHH!
(FOOTSTEPS)
[MAN 1] IS THAT THE PRINCESS?
[MAN 2] IT'S ACTUALLY
THE PRINCESS!
[RAYNESHIA] UH!
(RAYNESHIA GASPS)
(CROWD CHEERING)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
UH! OH, MY GOD.
WHAT... WHAT AM I GONNA SAY?
[KRUSTY] HMM.
(RAYNESHIA INHALES, SIGHS)
EVERYONE. IT'S NICE
TO MEET YOU.
I AM AN ENVOY
FROM MY GRANDFATHER,
THE HIGH LORD SERJIAD COWEN,
THE LEADER OF EASTAL'S
FREEDOM CITIES.
I AM PRINCESS RAYNESHIA
EL‐ARTE COWEN.
I AM HERE TO MAKE A
REQUEST OF YOU TODAY.
IT GOES BEYOND MASTER
SHIROE'S EXPLANATION.
ALL OF THE YAMATO ISLAND
CHAIN IS IN GRAVE DANGER,
AND WE CAN NO LONGER
CALL UPON OUR GUARDIANS,
THE IZUMO KNIGHTS.
THIS SITUATION HAS PUT
US IN THE POSITION
TO HAVE TO DEAL WITH THE
ASSAULT FROM THE GOBLIN
ARMIES ON OUR OWN.
I'M ASHAMED TO
ADMIT THIS TO YOU,
BUT EVEN MY GRANDFATHER
AND HIS COURT
HAVE NOT COME TO AGREE
ON WHAT THE PROPER COURSE
OF ACTION SHOULD BE.
EVEN MORE THAN THAT...
DURING OUR RECENT
DIPLOMATIC CONFERENCE,
WE ACTUALLY TRIED TO FORCE YOU
TO PERFORM OUR OWN DUTIES
TO PROTECT OUR CITIES.
WE WERE PREPARED TO DEMAND
THIS FROM ALL OF YOU.
AS IF THE ADVENTURERS,
LIKE ALWAYS,
WERE JUST GOING TO
ACCEPT OUR ORDERS
TO FIGHT FOR US
WITHOUT QUESTION.
FOR THIS, I AM...
I AM TERRIBLY SORRY
FOR THIS ASSUMPTION.
AND ALSO, I MUST APOLOGIZE
TO YOU ONCE AGAIN,
BECAUSE I HAVE ANOTHER SELFISH
REQUEST TO MAKE OF ALL OF YOU.
WE HAVE NOTHING TO OFFER
IN THE WAY OF COMPENSATION
FOR WHAT I'M ABOUT TO ASK.
WHEN I LOOK AROUND AT ALL
OF YOU, I START TO UNDERSTAND.
THERE'S NOTHING
I REALLY CAN OFFER.
YOU'RE ALREADY SO PROSPEROUS.
YOU'RE ALREADY FREE IN THE
TRUEST SENSE OF THE WORD.
AND I CAN'T GIVE YOU
ANYTHING BETTER THAN THAT.
BUT PLEASE, AS A DAUGHTER
AND HEIR OF THE COWEN FAMILY,
I HAVE A DUTY TO MY PEOPLE
TO PROTECT OUR CITY.
I'M NOT VERY BRAVE...
I'M LAZY...
AND AN ORNAMENT WITH A TITLE.
BUT IN SPITE OF THAT,
I'M GOING TO FIGHT!
(CROWD MURMURING)
(KRUSTY AND SHIROE CHUCKLE)
IN THE END, I HAVE NO CHOICE.
ALL I CAN OFFER IS MY THANKS,
AND I CAN ONLY HOPE IT'S ENOUGH.
WILL YOU FIGHT BY MY SIDE,
IN THE NAME OF YOUR GOODWILL,
PEACE, AND FREEDOM?
IF SO, I WILL DO EVERYTHING
IN MY POWER TO PROTECT THE
FREEDOM OF ALL ADVENTURERS.
PLEASE. PLEASE, HELP ME.
(WHIMPERS)
(BANG)
UHH.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(HORNS BLOWING)
(SHOUTING)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
[CROWD, CHANTING] PRINCESS!
PRINCESS! PRINCESS!
WE SHALL MAKE THIS OUR
FIRST MILITARY EXPEDITION.
THE ROUND TABLE HAS
ISSUED THIS QUEST.
AND ALL ADVENTURERS ABOVE
LEVEL 40 ARE WELCOME.
IF YOU WISH TO VOLUNTEER,
PLEASE COME FORWARD.
I, KRUSTY, WILL
LEAD THE FORCES.
(CROWD CHEERING)
AND I, SHIROE,
AM THE STRATEGIST.
THE FIRST GROUP IS A
FORWARD STRIKE BATTALION.
VOLUNTEERS, STAND BY.
I WILL CONTACT YOU
WITH FURTHER ORDERS.
[KRUSTY] THAT IS ALL.
REST UP UNTIL THEN.
DISMISSED.
(CROWD CHEERING)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
WHAT DID... I DO?
[KRUSTY] WHAT ARE YOU
ALL FLUSTERED ABOUT NOW?
[RAYNESHIA] UH! UH! WHAT IN
THE HECK ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?!
A NOBLE SHOULDN'T STAND UP IN
FRONT OF A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
TELLING EVERYONE
HER WEAKNESSES!
PRINCESS, YOU
DID VERY WELL.
HUH? ARE YOU
SURE IT WORKED?
LET'S GO. OK?
[RAYNESHIA] UHH.
[SHIROE] IN THIS OPERATION,
OUR PRIMARY CONCERN IS SPEED.
[TAKAYAMA] WHY IS THAT?
WE CAN'T BE SURE
WHAT THE GOBLINS
WILL DO AFTER THIS,
BUT I HAVE A GUESS.
ONCE THEY'RE DONE EATING
THEIR FILL IN THE MOUNTAINS,
THEY'RE PROBABLY
HEADED HERE.
[AKATSUKI] THEN THE CITY
WOULD BECOME A WAR ZONE.
[TAKAYAMA] YOU'RE SAYING THAT'S
JUST ONE POSSIBILITY, RIGHT?
KNOWING WHAT THEY WANT
TO HIT GIVES THEM THE
ADVANTAGE, FOR NOW.
THAT'S A FACT.
SO, WE HAVE TO MOVE
FASTER THAN THEM.
[TAKAYAMA] IN THAT CASE,
WE SHOULD PROBABLY HAVE
THE ADVENTURERS
LEAVE AS SOON AS THEY'RE READY.
[SHIROE] YES.
[AKATSUKI]
I UNDERSTAND,
MY LORD.
THAT WOULD BE WHY WE'RE USING
THE STEAMSHIP, ISN'T IT?
[SHIROE] IT MIGHT NOT BE IDEAL
TO GET EVERYTHING DONE,
BUT IT WILL GET FIRST
BATTALION TO NARASHINO
PORT AS FAST AS WE CAN.
WE CAN COME BACK
FOR MORE AFTERWARDS.
KRUSTY, I'LL LEAVE
THE OCYPETE TO YOU.
[KRUSTY] RIGHT. AND
YOU'RE DOING WHAT?
I HAVE SOMETHING
GOING ON.
[MICHITAKA] THE MIDRAUNT
EQUESTRIAN PARK?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐CHAT] YES.
THERE ARE ONLY WILD
ANIMALS IN THAT AREA,
AND NONE OF THOSE MONSTERS.
THE LOCATION'S IDEAL
TO SET UP A HEADQUARTERS.
[MICHITAKA]
HOW MANY PEOPLE?
[SHIROE] AROUND 1,200.
[MICHITAKA] 1,200? JEEZ.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU GOT THAT MANY.
[SHIROE] THE PRINCESS TOOK
A CHANCE AND IT PAID OFF.
[MICHITAKA] I GUESS SO.
[SHIROE] WE'LL BE THERE
THIS AFTERNOON AND WE
CAN WATER OUR HORSES.
AND ONCE THAT SHIP DROPS ANCHOR,
WE CAN FIGURE OUT WHO
BELONGS IN WHAT GROUPS
AND WITH WHAT SKILLS.
[MICHITAKA] I'LL CONTINUE
TO KEEP AN EYE ON OUR
NOBLEMEN FRIENDS.
SORRY YOU'RE HAVING
TO DO ALL THIS ALONE.
[SHIROE] NOT AT ALL.
THANK YOU.
[MICHITAKA] UHH. I WANTED
THE CHANCE TO SEE THE
OCYPETE LEAVE PORT.
[HENRIETTA] MICHITAKA?
[MICHITAKA] HUH?
[HENRIETTA] SOMEONE'S
HERE FOR YOU.
A VISITOR?
[SERJIAD] MY GRANDDAUGHTER'S
ACTIONS RISK SPLITTING THE
SOLIDARITY OF THE LEAGUE.
[MICHITAKA] I ASSUME THEY'RE
CONCERNED THAT THE COWEN FAMILY
HAS BEEN WORKING SECRETLY
WITH THE ROUND TABLE
ON A SEPARATE DEAL?
[SERJIAD] INDEED.
WELL, I'M SURE THE PRINCESS
HAD NO SUCH DESIGNS.
I'M AFRAID HER INTENTIONS
ARE NOT RELEVANT.
THE LORDS WILL ALLOW
THEIR PERCEPTIONS TO
LEAD THEIR ACTIONS.
[MICHITAKA] I UNDERSTAND.
AND THEY PROBABLY BELIEVE
THAT MAIHAMA IS TRYING
TO ESTABLISH MORE POWER
WITH AKIHABARA AT ITS SIDE.
THAT IS A POSSIBILITY, CORRECT?
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
ON THE MATTER?
WHERE DO YOUR PEOPLE STAND?
WHERE DO WE STAND?
UHH. HUH.
MM. WHY DON'T WE LISTEN TO
WHAT YOU HAVE IN MIND FIRST,
LORD SERJIAD?
[HENRIETTA] WE DON'T KNOW
IF THE ROUND TABLE'S
IN A POSITION TO ACCEPT
A PROPOSAL LIKE THAT.
[MICHITAKA] HEH.
[SERJIAD] HMM.
I CAN SEE YOUR POINT OF VIEW.
[MICHITAKA] LOOK, I'M SORRY,
BUT I GOTTA SAY THIS.
WE'RE NEVER GONNA GET ANYWHERE
IF WE KEEP QUESTIONING
EACH OTHER'S INTENTIONS.
HONESTLY, WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO GET FROM ALL THIS?
[SERJIAD] HMM.
FIRST I'D LIKE TO SEE
THE GOBLINS EXTERMINATED.
THE PROTECTION OF OUR
PEOPLE IS A NECESSITY.
ALL RIGHT. I CAN
APPRECIATE THAT.
SO, WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU
THINK WE SHOULD DO HERE?
[SERJIAD] WELL, I HAVE
ABANDONED THE IDEA OF HAVING
THE ROUND TABLE JOIN THE LEAGUE
AS A MEMBER OF NOBILITY.
[HENRIETTA AND MICHITAKA] HUH?
[SERJIAD] IN FACT,
I WOULD LIKE TO
APOLOGIZE FOR OFFERING YOU
A NOBLE TITLE IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
IT WAS RUDE OF ME TO
OFFER SUCH A POSITION.
I UNDERSTAND NOW
THAT THE ROUND TABLE
AND THE COMMUNITY OF
AKIHABARA ARE FORCES
THAT RIVAL EASTAL IN
BOTH STRENGTH OF FORCE
AND ITS STABILITY OF STRUCTURE.
IN THE END, IT WOULD
NEVER HAVE BEEN POSSIBLE
TO TRY TO MAKE YOUR PEOPLE A
COHESIVE PART OF OUR ALLIANCE.
SO, HOW DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD
PROCEED, MOVING FORWARD?
[SERJIAD] I WOULD THINK IT BEST
TO MAKE A NON‐AGGRESSION PACT
AND CREATE A FORMAL TRADE TREATY
AND USE IT AS THE BASIS
FOR FURTHER RELATIONS.
IF WE COULD TAKE
EACH OTHER'S HANDS
AS SIMPLE NEIGHBORS?
THAT WOULD BE A PRETTY
GOOD PLACE TO START.
THERE'S ONE THING...
THE ISSUE WITH THE GOBLINS
IS GOING TO BE A RECURRING ONE.
WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS
CONCERNING THE INEQUALITY
BETWEEN OUR TWO DEFENSES?
[SERJIAD] THE INEQUALITY
BETWEEN ADVENTURERS
AND PEOPLE OF THE LAND?
HMM.
[MICHITAKA] UHH...
[HENRIETTA] OH. OH.
[MICHITAKA] WELL, WE DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT NOW.
WITHOUT KRUSTY,
THE PRINCESS, AND SHIROE,
WE CAN'T REALLY MAKE
THOSE SORTS OF DECISIONS,
SO, LET'S WAIT
FOR THEIR INPUT.
WHY DON'T WE JUST TABLE THAT
DISCUSSION FOR ANOTHER TIME?
(MICHITAKA AND HENRIETTA LAUGH)
[SERJIAD] HMM.
UHH. I'M SURE
SHIROE CAN FIND A WAY
TO WORK ALL OF
THE LOGISTICS OUT.
RIGHT. VERY WELL.
THEN I SHALL HAVE MY
GRANDDAUGHTER HANDLE THIS.
RAYNESHIA CAN TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE
NEGOTIATIONS MOVING FORWARD.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(FIREWORKS REPORT)
(SIGH)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
RUNNING INTO THAT MEETING AND
RAISING MY VOICE TO EVERYONE?
THEN I GO AND HUMILIATE
GRANDFATHER AND THE FAMILY
AND JUST GO RUNNING OFF?
THEN I GAVE A SPEECH IN FRONT
OF A BUNCH OF STRANGERS IN
THESE EMBARRASSING CLOTHES.
I GOT SO SWEPT UP, I JUST
SAID WHATEVER CAME TO MIND.
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE WANTS
TO FORGET ALL ABOUT THIS
AND GO BACK TO HER COMFY BED.
THAT... THAT'S REALLY
NOT TRUE, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE NOT SOUNDING
VERY CONFIDENT.
MM.
[KRUSTY] AND YOU LOOK
KIND OF MISERABLE.
[RAYNESHIA] I SAID
WHAT I NEEDED TO.
BUT I'M AWARE OF THE FACT THAT
YOU'RE RISKING YOUR LIVES TODAY,
SO, IT'S ONLY NATURAL THAT
I SHOULD JOIN THE FIGHT
AND SHARE THOSE RISKS
WITH ALL OF YOU.
[KRUSTY] HMM.
EVER SINCE
I WENT TO AKIHABARA,
I GUESS I'VE BEEN...
I'VE BEEN FEELING DOWN.
[KRUSTY] FEELING DOWN?
[RAYNESHIA] I WAS LOST THERE...
NOT RECOGNIZING
ANYTHING OR KNOWING
WHAT YOUR WORLD WAS LIKE.
I REALLY WAS A BIRD IN
A GILDED CAGE, WASN'T I?
WHERE I COME FROM,
WOMEN DON'T HAVE ANY REAL
POLITICAL POWER TO SPEAK OF.
BUT OF COURSE, THERE I WENT,
PROMISING TO PROTECT
PEOPLE'S FREEDOMS.
NO ONE IS EVER GOING
TO LET ME DO THAT.
BUT YOU KNOW, YOU WERE THE FIRST
TO ACKNOWLEDGE MY FREEDOM
AND TAKE ME INTO
BATTLE WITH YOU.
SO, I WANT TO PROTECT
THEIR FREEDOM IF I CAN.
I WANT IT MORE THAN ANYTHING.
OF COURSE, IF I END
UP DYING OUT THERE,
WHAT I CAN AND CAN'T
DO WON'T MATTER.
[KRUSTY] YOU'LL BE FINE.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH? WHAT?
[KRUSTY] LISTEN, IT'S MORE‐
[TAKAYAMA] THE FORMATIONS
ARE IN POSITION
AND READY, MY LORD.
[KRUSTY] RIGHT. THANK YOU, MISA.
WE'LL TALK MORE LATER.
[MARIELLE] OH, GOODY, GOODY.
WELCOME BACK!
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE SAFE!
YEAH, YEAH,
I MISSED YOU, TOO,
BUT I CAN'T BREATHE,
MARIELLE!
YOU GUYS WERE
GREAT OUT THERE.
I'M, LIKE, REALLY
PROUD OF YOU.
[TOYA] YEAH, WELL,
WE DO WHAT WE CAN.
WELL, I SUPPOSE WE DID
ALL RIGHT, DIDN'T WE?
THANKS A LOT,
MISS MARIELLE.
[NAOTSUGU] COME ON. GO AHEAD
AND DO SOME BRAGGING.
[TOYA] I DON'T THINK SO.
WE STILL HAVE A LOT MORE
FIGHTING TO DO.
[NAOTSUGU] I GUESS WE CAN
SAY WE MADE IT THROUGH
THE FIRST MISSION, ANYWAY.
WE DID MANAGE TO KEEP CHOSHI
FROM GETTING TOTALLY CLOBBERED.
[MARIELLE] THE CAMP COUNSELORS
REALLY DID A SUPER JOB,
BUT THE NEW PLAYERS TOTALLY MADE
AN IMPACT IN THE BATTLES.
I WAS, LIKE, WONDERING
HOW I WAS GONNA ASK THEM
TO JOIN THE FIGHT,
BUT I REALLY DIDN'T NEED TO.
IT TURNED OUT THAT THEY
WANTED TO GO OUT THERE
AND GO FIGHT ON THEIR OWN.
DARN TOOTIN'
THEY DID.
WHEN IT COMES
DOWN TO IT,
IT WAS SUPER SHOCKING
TO ME TO FIND OUT
ALL THOSE PEOPLE OF THE
LAND HAVE THOUGHTS AND
FEELINGS JUST LIKE US.
IT'S REALLY BEAUTIFUL.
THE WHOLE THING CAUGHT
ME BY SURPRISE, TOO.
BUT HEY, SHIROE SAW
IT BEFORE WE DID.
THEY REALLY ARE
HUMAN BEINGS, RIGHT?
AND ALL OF US
REALLY ARE GUESTS.
WE HAVE TO REALLY CHANGE THE
WAY WE LOOK AT WHERE WE ARE.
IT'S LIKE THE MORE
GAMES YOU'VE PLAYED,
THE HARDER IT IS TO ACCEPT
ALL THIS AS REALITY.
(CROWD CHATTER)
[MARIELLE] AND ALL THESE KIDS
NEVER KNEW THE OLD GAME
LIKE WE DID.
SO, IT WAS EASY FOR THEM
TO JUST LOOK AT THEM
LIKE THEY WERE REAL PEOPLE.
TOTALLY.
OK. EVERYONE,
WE'VE ALMOST DONE IT.
LET'S ALL PROTECT
THE TOWN OF CHOSHI.
ALL RIGHT! I KNOW
YOU CAN DO IT,
SO, LIKE, LET'S GIVE IT
OUR BEST, EVERYONE!
(CROWD CHEERING)
[TOYA] YEAH!
LET'S DO IT!
[MINORI]
COME ON, GUYS!
[RUDY] I HAVE
SO GOT THIS.
THIS IS WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE AN ADVENTURER!
[ISUZU] HMM?
BUT RUDY...
[KRUSTY] STAND BY FOR
FORMATION ASSIGNMENTS!
(CROWD CHEERS)
[TAKAYAMA] OK, HERE'S THE PLAN.
WE WILL BE FIGHTING
IN LEGION RAIDS.
WE WILL FORM 4 GROUPS
CONSISTING OF 24 MEMBERS EACH,
MAKING 96 IN ALL.
IS 96 GOING
TO BE ENOUGH?
WITH A FORCE
THAT LARGE,
IT'S HARD TO FIGHT
AS A SINGLE UNIT,
AND ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE TO
GRASP THE OVERALL BATTLE.
[TAKAYAMA] IT WILL REQUIRE A LOT
OF EXPERIENCE TO COMMAND THEM.
BUT IN THAT RESPECT,
MY LORD IS THE BEST THERE IS.
[TAKAYAMA] TO BE HONEST,
IT IS WHERE HE EXCELS.
IN YAMATO, HE'S ONE OF
FEWER THAN 20 PEOPLE TO HAVE
COMMANDED AN ENTIRE ARMY.
HIS EXPERIENCE, INSTINCTS,
AND POWERS OF CONCENTRATION
ALL COMBINE IN A WAY TO MAKE
HIM THE ULTIMATE COMMANDER.
[RAYNESHIA]
I UNDERSTAND,
I GUESS.
[TAKAYAMA] ONE MORE THING.
[RAYNESHIA] HUH?
[TAKAYAMA] I AM GIVING YOU
A GUARD OF 12 MEN.
BUT EVEN SO, PLEASE REFRAIN
FROM DOING ANYTHING
FOOLISH, MY LADY.
YOU DO UNDERSTAND ME, YES?
YES, I DO.
[KRUSTY] WE'RE GETTING OFF AT
THE ABANDONED NARASHINO PORT.
FROM THERE, WE'RE GOING TO
THE WEST SIDE OF KASUMI LAKE,
SO WE HAVE 15 MILES TO COVER.
THEN, WE HEAD NORTH.
AND AS FAR AS THE GOBLINS GO...
[RAYNESHIA] UH.
SPARE NONE OF THEM.
(CROWD CHEERS)
(THUNDER)
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
THERE WAS A YOUNG PERSON
WHO WANTED TO CHANGE.
THEY THOUGHT AND THOUGHT,
AND FOUGHT AS HARD AS THEIR
SOUL AND STRENGTH WOULD ALLOW.
THEY WANTED TO PROTECT SOMEONE,
AND THAT'S ALL THEY
EVER REALLY WANTED.
EVEN IF THAT MEANT
SACRIFICING THEIR OWN LIFE.
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.