(PANTING)
[MAN] CATCH YOUR
BREATH THERE, BOY.
(BOY EXHALES)
[MAN] LOOKS LIKE
IT'S EAST.
HEY, POPS, HAVE
YOU EVER SEEN AN
ADVENTURER UP CLOSE?
[POPS] HMPH.
[BOY] I HEARD A RUMOR
ONCE THAT AN ADVENTURER
YOUNGER THAN ME
SKIPPED RIGHT OVER THIS
MOUNTAIN, HUMMING A TUNE.
I'D REALLY LOVE TO BE ABLE
TO DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT!
[POPS] DON'T BOTHER.
WHAT CAN THEY DO?
CAN THEY LIVE AS ONE
WITH THE LAND?
ADVENTURERS CREATE NOTHING.
THEY SIMPLY FIGHT
AND SHED BLOOD.
HUH?
[BOY] WHAT IS IT, POPS?
[POPS] SHH.
[BOY] OHH...
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
[POPS] OH, NO.
THAT LOOKS BAD.
WE HAVE TO GET BACK
AND TELL THE VILLAGE.
(WHIMPERING)
[SMASH]
AH, HERE YOU GO!
(NYAN‐TA WHISTLES)
[NYAN‐TA] OH, YEAH!
I DEFINITELY NEED TO BRING
THE WHOLE GUILD HERE NEXT TIME.
(TOYA GRUNTS)
COME GET SOME!
HEAD SPLITTER!
I DID IT!
(ELECTRICAL SOUND)
HUH? HEY, I'M STUCK!
HELP ME!
PURIFICATION BARRIER!
[TOYA] HUH?!
ASSASSINATION!
AURA SABER!
[TOYA] UHH...
[MINORI] HUH...
[TOYA]
SORRY, GUYS. I, UH‐
[NAOTSUGU] SAMURAI ATTACKS HAVE
A LONG COOL DOWN, LITTLE MAN.
AND AFTER YOU CAST A
STRONG SPELL, YOU MIGHT
NOT BE ABLE TO MOVE.
BET YOU FORGOT ABOUT THAT.
[TOYA] I REMEMBERED IT,
REALLY. I JUST...
SHIROE ASKED US TO
WATCH OUT FOR YOU
DURING YOUR TRAINING.
DON'T EXPECT US
TO GO EASY ON YOU.
[TOYA AND MINORI]
THANK YOU, SENSEI.
[NAOTSUGU]
NEXT TOPIC.
MAN TO MAN, TOYA.
YOU SEE, CHICKS ARE LIKE‐
(NAOTSUGU WAILS)
[TOYA] LIKE WHAT?
[AKATSUKI] NAOTSUGU IS A MORON.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
[MINORI] SENSEI...
[NAOTSUGU] AS FOR YOU, MINORI,
WE'LL DO OUR BEST,
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WE CAN TEACH YOU ABOUT
BEING A SHRINE PRIEST.
[MINORI] THAT'S OK.
HE TOLD ME EVERYTHING
I NEED TO KNOW.
(GRUMBLES)
[NYAN‐TA] SHIROECHI?
[SHIROE] UH, HEY, CHIEF.
YOU PULLED YOURSELF ANOTHER
ALL‐NIGHTER, DIDN'T YOU?
NOT TRUE. I MANAGED
A LITTLE BIT OF SLEEP.
[NYAN‐TA] TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE NICE DAY.
GO OUTSIDE. DO SOMETHING
ELSE FOR A WHILE.
SEE SOME OF
AKIHABARA'S NEW STUFF.
[SHIROE] I'D LOVE TO,
BUT I'VE GOT OTHER THINGS
OCCUPYING MY MIND RIGHT NOW.
[NYAN‐TA] AND BY THAT,
YOU MEAN SOME WAY TO
GET US ALL HOME, HUH?
YEAH, THAT, TOO.
BUT EVEN IN A WORLD LIKE THIS
THAT USED TO BE A GAME FOR US,
THAT OLD SAYING ABOUT KNOWLEDGE
BEING POWER STILL WORKS.
[NYAN‐TA] WHAT DO YOU
HAVE HERE, HMM?
[SHIROE] IF A COOK PREPARES
FOOD WITH HIS OWN HANDS,
AND A CRAFTSMAN MAKES
THINGS WITH NOTHING BUT
TOOLS AND HIS WITS,
THEN WE'VE ALREADY SEEN
THAT WE CAN DO THINGS
THE GAME NEVER COULD.
[NYAN‐TA] AH, SO YOU'RE
TRYING TO SEE IF YOU
CAN GET THE SAME RESULTS
FROM YOUR SKILLS
AS A SCRIBE, HUH?
I WAS ABLE TO DRAW UP
A SIMPLE CONTRACT.
I WONDER IF THERE ARE
OTHER APPLICATIONS FOR IT.
(CHIME)
HMM?
HEY, HENRIETTA.
[HENRIETTA]
SHIROE, I CAN'T
HANDLE THIS ANYMORE!
SAVE ME!
[SHIROE] HUH?
I WANT TO GO!
[MARIELLE] I WANT TO EAT!
[SHIROE] OH, WOW.
[HENRIETTA] UGH!
SO I GUESS ALL OF US
GOT A CALL, HUH?
[TOYA] SURE DID, MAN.
[NYAN‐TA] ALL RIGHT, WHAT'S
ALL THE COMMOTION IN HERE?
WELL, IT'S KIND OF LIKE‐
IT'S SUMMER.
IT'S SUMMER IN THE
ELDER TALES WORLD!
AND SUMMER IS ALL
ABOUT THE BEACH,
SNOW CONES, WATERMELON,
RAMEN, AND CURRY RICE!
LIKE, TOTALLY, RIGHT?
LET ME GO TO THE BEACH!
[MARIELLE] I WANT TO
HAVE A SNOW CONE...
[HENRIETTA] STOP THIS!
THE CRESCENT MOON ALLIANCE
IS ONE OF THE ROUND TABLE'S
11 ESTEEMED GUILDS,
AND YOU ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE ITS GUILD MASTER.
(MARIELLE WHIMPERS)
LOOKS LIKE AKIHABARA STILL
HAS A LOT OF PROBLEMS.
WE PROBABLY SHOULDN'T LEAVE
IT RIGHT NOW, SHOULD WE?
[MARIELLE]
I'VE WORKED REALLY HARD.
(CRYING) I'M STILL
WORKING REALLY HARD!
ALL I REALLY WANT IS SOME
REST AND RECREATION!
[HENRIETTA] YOU COME DOWN HERE
THIS INSTANT, MARIELLE!
[NYAN‐TA] I WOULD DARE SAY
THAT THE LADY IS IN A
RATHER DIRE NEED OF A
CHANGE OF PACE, HMM?
THE BEACH, HUH?
[ISUZU] WHAT'S THIS?
A NEW QUEST?
OK, WAIT.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
"ROUND TABLE‐SPONSORED TRAINING
CAMP FOR NEW PLAYERS"?
[PLAYER] A SUMMER
TRAINING CAMP FOR NEW
PLAYERS UNDER LEVEL 40?
HOW DELIGHTFULLY
BOURGEOIS OF OUR NEW
LEVEL‐90 BENEFACTORS.
HUH! HA HA HA!
IT'S TIME! THEY FINALLY
CREATED A STAGE LARGE
ENOUGH TO ACCOMMODATE ME.
AT LONG LAST, EVERYONE
WILL WITNESS MY PROWESS!
EVERYONE WILL BOW
TO THE MAGNIFICENT NAME
"RUNDELLHAUS CODE"!
[MARIELLE]
THIS IS A SUPER IDEA.
[HENRIETTA]
IT'S PERFECT EXCUSE
FOR A VACATION.
[MARIELLE]
BEACH TRAINING CAMP!
[HENRIETTA] MARIELLE!
WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT TRAINING NOOBS,
AND MARIELLE NEEDED TO GET
OUT OF THE GUILD BUILDING.
TWO BIRDS,
ONE STONE, BRO.
FOR DARK, SINISTER SHIROE,
COMING UP WITH A PLAN LIKE THIS
IS REALLY NO
BIG DEAL AT ALL.
[SHIROE]
"DARK, SINISTER SHIROE"?
YOU'RE A GOOD,
"SINISTER," SHIROE...
AND SO ARE YOU, BIG,
STRONG NAOTSUGU!
[NAOTSUGU] AH, GET OFF OF ME!
[NYAN‐TA] SO WILL YOU
BE GOING, AS WELL, HMM?
[SERARA]
YES, I AM.
UM... I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU ARE, TOO?
I WILL BE ASSISTING THE OTHERS
WITH YOUR TRAINING PROGRAM, DIG?
(FAWNING)
[ALL]
SHE'S SO OBVIOUS.
[NYAN‐TA] COOL.
[TOYA] SHIROE AND ALL HIS
FRIENDS ARE GONNA BE THERE.
[MINORI] YEAH.
[TOYA] I'VE GOT TO DO
THE BEST I CAN. HA!
[TOYA] YAH!
[MINORI, THINKING]
I GUESS PART OF ME WAS
ALWAYS DOWN ON MYSELF
FOR NOT BEING ABLE TO
DO ANYTHING FOR TOYA.
I REALLY THOUGHT THERE WAS
SOMETHING I COULD'VE DONE
OR SHOULD'VE DONE FOR HIM,
AND I JUST COULDN'T OR
DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO DO IT.
BUT THAT JUST ISN'T
THE CASE ANYMORE.
NOW IT'S UP TO ME TO
MAKE SURE SHIROE KNOWS
HE DID THE RIGHT THING BY
SAVING US AND LETTING
US JOIN HIS GUILD.
HMM.
[KAYU]
MAN, NOTHING'S
BITING TODAY.
HUH?
(HOOFBEATS)
WHAT'S GOING ON?
[AKATSUKI] SO THIS IS
WHERE THE TRAINING CAMP
WILL BE HELD, MY LORD?
[SHIROE]
THE TOWN OF CHOSHI IN
THE ZANTLEAF REGION.
[HENRIETTA]
KARASHIN HAS ALREADY GONE
AND LOOKED AT THE AREA,
AND HE HAS ALREADY MANAGED
TO SPEAK WITH THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND THERE, AS WELL.
WAY TO HANDLE
BUSINESS, MAN.
[HENRIETTA] SHORYU OF
OUR GUILD AND REZARICK
FROM THE BLACK SWORDS
WILL BE PARTICIPATING
AS TRAINERS.
[SHIROE] THAT'S FINE, BUT‐
[NAOTSUGU] UH.
NOW ALL I NEED IS SOME SPF
50 TO KEEP THE SUN OFF!
IT'S TOO
EARLY FOR THAT.
YOU KNOW THE CAMP ISN'T
UNTIL NEXT MONTH, MARIELLE.
I HAVE A SUMMER DRESS FOR YOU,
MY DARLING AKATSUKI!
[AKATSUKI] OH, COME ON!
[NAOTSUGU] MAYBE WE NEED
TO PUSH UP THE DATE.
[SHIROE] YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
[HENRIETTA] I SWEAR IT!
(SHORYU GASPS)
(CHIME)
[HENRIETTA]
DID YOU FIND SUNSCREEN?
[SHIROE] NO. THERE WERE A LOT
OF PEOPLE OUTSIDE THE GATES
I HADN'T SEEN BEFORE.
[HENRIETTA] HUH?
[MAN 1] WHAT IS GOING ON?
[MAN 2] DO YOU REMEMBER
THINGS LIKE THIS IN THE GAME?
[MAN 1] NO, NOT REALLY.
[SHORYU] THAT'S THEM.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, OK.
LIKE, WHY DOES THAT DUDE
WITH THE FUNKY HAT
LOOK FAMILIAR TO ME?
[NAOTSUGU] WHAT THE HECK?
[AKATSUKI] WHAT'S
GOING ON, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] THEY'RE ALL
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[MARIELLE]
SO THAT MEANS...
[SHIROE]
A HERALD OF ROYALTY.
[HERALD] I AM THE EMISSARY
OF DUKE SERJIAD COWEN,
HIGH LORD OF EASTAL'S
LEAGUE OF FREEDOM CITIES.
I HAVE COME HERE TO GAIN
AUDIENCE WITH THE LEADER OF
THE ROUND TABLE CONFERENCE.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IN "ELDER TALES,"
JAPAN IS CALLED YAMATO.
IT'S DIVIDED INTO
5 MAJOR TERRITORIES.
THE LEAGUE OF FREEDOM
CITIES OF EASTAL
IS AN ALLIANCE OF LORDS
THAT RULE EASTERN JAPAN,
AND EASTAL HAS SENT AN
EMISSARY TO THE ROUND TABLE.
THEY WANT US TO ATTEND
THEIR NEXT GATHERING
OF ALLIED NOBLES,
AND CURIOUSLY, THERE'S
ALSO A DANCE INVOLVED.
(HOOFBEATS)
[KRUSTY] AND I SUPPOSE YOU
ANTICIPATED THIS, TOO?
[SHIROE] THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
SHOULD BE WELL AWARE OF OUR
ESTABLISHING THE ROUND TABLE.
SO, YES, THIS MOVE
ISN'T UNEXPECTED.
THEY SAID THEY WERE
PREPARED TO GRANT TITLES
OF NOBILITY TO SOME OF US.
IT'S NOT AN
EASY CHOICE,
WHETHER OR NOT WE GO THERE
TO REPRESENT OURSELVES.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
NOT EASY?
OBVIOUSLY WE CAN
START NETWORKING WITH
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND,
AND WE SHOULDN'T PASS IT UP,
ESPECIALLY WHEN THERE'S A
CHANCE TO LEARN MORE ABOUT
THIS WORLD THAN WE DO.
SO WHAT'S THE DOWNSIDE?
[SHIROE] WE MAY VERY WELL GET
CAUGHT UP IN THEIR POLITICS.
IF WE DON'T PARTICIPATE, THAT
POSSIBILITY GOES AWAY, BUT...
[KRUSTY] WE LOSE A CHANCE
TO GAIN VALUABLE INFORMATION.
[SHIROE]
THAT'S THE TRADEOFF.
[KRUSTY] IS THERE A CHANCE
OF WAR WITH THEM?
[SHIROE]
IT'S NOT LIKELY.
THERE'S NO ONE IN THEIR
RANKS THAT WE KNOW OF
WHO'S ANYWHERE NEAR AS
STRONG AS AN ADVENTURER...
CERTAINLY NOT LEVEL 90s LIKE US.
[KRUSTY] ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT DO YOU HAVE
IN MIND? I'M LISTENING.
HMM.
[MARIELLE] OHH, I CAN SMELL
THE SALT ON THE AIR!
[NAOTSUGU] IT'S WAY DIFFERENT
FROM AKIHABARA, ISN'T IT?
[TOYA] CHECK IT
OUT, MINORI. THERE!
[MINORI] WOW!
[NYAN‐TA] HMM.
SOME TREES, BUT MOSTLY
MEADOW AROUND HERE.
[SERARA] YEAH!
[TOYA] OH, YEAH.
THOSE LOOK GOOD!
[MINORI] NOW, TOYA, DON'T
TAKE ANY WITHOUT ASKING.
THAT WOULD BE
SIMPLY VULGAR,
BUT WHAT DO YOU EXPECT
FROM COMMONERS?
[TOYA] WHAT'D YOU SAY?!
[MINORI] TAKE IT EASY, TOYA.
[ISUZU] YOU'RE AS
LIVELY AS EVER, I SEE.
[MINORI]
HEY, ISUZU!
YOU KNOW, BACK IN
THE REAL WORLD,
YOU'D NEVER THINK OF
HOLDING A TRAINING CAMP
INSIDE THE GAME LIKE THIS.
(MINORI LAUGHS)
[MINORI AND TOYA] HUH?
[TOYA] IS SHE ONE OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
WHO LIVE AROUND HERE?
[ALL] HI!
[TOYA]
ARE THEY SERIOUS?!
[ISUZU]
ISN'T THIS A SCHOOL?
THIS IS WHERE WE'RE
GONNA BE STAYING
EVERY NIGHT? AWESOME!
AND TONIGHT WE'RE HAVING
A BARBECUE OUTSIDE!
(CROWD CHEERS)
[TOYA] I SURE WISH
BROTHER SHIROE WOULD'VE
COME WITH US, MINORI.
[MINORI] YEAH.
HE HAS AN IMPORTANT CONFERENCE
WITH ONE OF THE GOVERNMENTS
OF THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[MINORI]
HE'S GOT TO BE THERE.
I WONDER IF THE KIDS IN
CAMP ARE DOING OK.
HEY, I LEFT MY BRAND‐NEW
STEAM ENGINE BEHIND TO
GO ON THIS TRIP OF YOURS.
[MICHITAKA] KEEP YOUR HEAD
IN THE GAME, MASTERMIND.
[SHIROE]
OK. I GOT IT.
[KARASHIN]
I UNDERSTAND.
WE NEED TO SEND A PARTY THERE
TO SEE IF WE CAN GET MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT THEM.
[ISAAC] IT'S REALLY CUTE THAT
THEY WANT TO MAKE US NOBLES,
LIKE THEY'RE BETTER THAN
US IN THE FIRST PLACE.
WHO DOES THOSE NPC'S
THINK THEY ARE?
FOR ONE THING,
THEY'RE NOT JUST
SOFTWARE ANYMORE.
I THOUGHT WE
DISCUSSED THAT FACT
AT LENGTH ALREADY.
[ISAAC]
SORRY. IT'S JUST HABIT.
[SHIROE] WE'RE ALL IN
AGREEMENT ABOUT GOING TO
THE CONFERENCE IN EASTAL.
WE SHOULD BE SURE TO PUT
OUR BEST FOOT FORWARD
WHILE WE'RE THERE.
SO WHO'S GONNA REPRESENT
US AT THE MEETING?
THOSE DAYS OVERLAP WITH
THE TRAINING CAMP, YOU KNOW.
UH, I'M IN CHARGE OF THAT
TRAINING CAMP, SO I'M OUT.
[KARASHIN] WELL, SINCE D. D. D.
HAS THE MOST MEMBERS IN IT,
MAYBE KRUSTY SHOULD
REPRESENT US.
OK.
BUT D. D. D. ARE
PRIMARILY WARRIORS.
CRAFTING AND COMMERCE
SHOULD GO, TOO.
(KARASHIN GASPS)
[RODERICK] UH, YOU SEE,
WE'RE WORKING ON THE
OCTOPEDE RIGHT NOW
AND THE STEAM ENGINE TO RUN IT.
[KARASHIN] YEAH, AND I'VE
GOT A LOT OF OTHER STUFF
GOING ON MYSELF.
[MICHITAKA] AND I'M JUST GETTING
TO THE PART WHERE I MAKE
THIS THING MORE POWERFUL.
AN IMPASSE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
TO DO ABOUT IT.
[ALL] ROCK, PAPER...
[MICHITAKA] OH, CRAP.
[RODERICK] HA! YEAH!
AHEM, IT'S DECIDED, THEN.
[KARASHIN] MICHITAKA WILL
REPRESENT THE MERCHANT GUILDS.
[MARIELLE]
THAT WAS NICE OF HIM.
[KRUSTY] NO. THE TEAM'S
NOT COMPLETE YET.
I NEED SOMEONE WITH A KNACK
FOR POLITICS AND STUDYING
THE OPPOSITION.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
[ALL] STARE...
[SHIROE] OK. I GOT IT.
[AKATSUKI] HMM.
SO THAT'S
WHAT HAPPENED?
[SHIROE] YOU ALWAYS HAVE
THE OPTION OF BEING
A TRAINER AT THE CAMP.
A SHINOBI SHOULD
FOLLOW HER MASTER NO
MATTER WHERE HE GOES.
[SHIROE] REALLY, NOW?
AND WHY EXACTLY ARE
YOU HERE, HENRIETTA?
[HENRIETTA]
I TOLD YOU...
I AM MERELY
PARTICIPATING AS
AN OBSERVER.
[SHIROE]
OK, MISS OBSERVER, SO WHAT'S
STICKING OUT OF YOUR BAG?
(HENRIETTA GASPS)
[HENRIETTA] OH, UH,
JUST SOME FABRIC.
IT MOST DEFINITELY IS NOT
A SUMMER DRESS FOR AKATSUKI!
[SHIROE] METHINKS THE LADY
DOTH PROTEST TOO MUCH.
YOU SLY DOG, YOU.
MAN, SHIROE,
HOW DO YOU DO IT?
[SHIROE] IT ISN'T
LIKE THAT, GUYS.
[KRUSTY] SO TELL ME,
WHAT INFORMATION ARE WE
CULLING FROM THESE PEOPLE?
SOME THINGS HAVE TO
HAVE MORE VALUE.
[SHIROE] EVERYTHING
WE CAN, I GUESS.
BUT IF I HAD TO
SET A PRIORITY,
IT'D BE ON WHETHER OR NOT
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
HAVE CHANGED AT ALL.
[MICHITAKA]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
BACK IN THE DAYS WHEN
ELDER TALES WAS NOTHING
BUT A GAME ENVIRONMENT,
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
WERE MADE BY THE
SOFTWARE DEVELOPERS
TO BE A WHOLE LOT WEAKER
THAN THE ADVENTURERS.
NOW, OF COURSE, THERE
WERE IN‐GAME EXCEPTIONS
LIKE THE PRECURSORS
AND THE ROYAL GUARD,
BUT RUN‐OF‐THE‐MILL NPCs
NEVER GOT STRONGER THAN
THE SOFTWARE LET THEM.
[MICHITAKA] WHEN ADVENTURERS
LIKE US DIE, WE JUST COME
BACK TO LIFE IN THE CATHEDRAL,
BUT PEOPLE OF THE LAND
BITE IT FOR GOOD.
[SHIROE] SO FAR, BUT WE CAN'T
BE SURE IF THE APOCALYPSE
HAS CHANGED THEM, AS WELL,
LIKE THE REST OF THIS "GAME."
[MARIELLE] SORRY TO DRAG YOU
ALONG WITH ME LIKE THIS.
[MINORI] NO, IT'S FINE.
[SHIROE] FOR ONE THING,
THEY AREN'T SIMPLE
NON‐PLAYER CHARACTERS ANYMORE.
THEIR EVOLUTION IS OBVIOUS.
NPC'S WERE A PROGRAMMED
PART OF THE GAME
DESIGNED TO HELP SEND
THE PLAYER ON QUESTS
THAT RESULT IN A PLAYER
RECEIVING GOLD, INVENTORY ITEMS,
AND OTHER THINGS OF VALUE.
THE MAGIC BAG IS
ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE THE
REWARD FOR ONE OF THE
BASIC QUESTS EVERYONE DOES.
IT HOLDS EVERYTHING.
HOWEVER, FROM THE LOOKS OF IT,
PEOPLE OF THE LAND
ARE NO LONGER GIVING ANY QUESTS
TO ANY ADVENTURERS ANYMORE.
[MISA] AND THAT MEANS
NONE OF THE NEW PLAYERS
WILL BE ABLE TO DO
EVEN THE SIMPLEST
QUESTS TO GET THEIR
INVENTORIES KICKSTARTED.
[SHIROE] THE POTENTIAL
BACKLASH FROM THAT COULD BE
EXTREMELY FAR‐REACHING.
[HENRIETTA] DID YOU TELL
MARIELLE ABOUT THIS?
[SHIROE] YEAH, I DID.
UH, WE'RE FACT‐FINDING?
[MARIELLE]
YEAH, SHIROE ASKED ME.
HE SAID TO "TALK TO
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND
AND LEARN AS MUCH AS YOU
CAN BY TALKING TO THEM..."
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
[MINORI] OH. SO THAT'S WHY YOU
SPOKE TO THE VILLAGE ELDER?
[MARIELLE] WELL, THAT
WASN'T THE ONLY REASON.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
I WAS JUST BEING POLITE.
THAT'S ONE WORTH NOTING...
SO SHIROE SENT YOU.
OH, WE DEFINITELY CAN'T
MESS THIS UP, THEN!
[MARIELLE] YOU'RE A
GOOD GIRL, YOU KNOW THAT?
[MINORI]
WHAT'S THAT FOR?!
[MARIELLE]
OH, I FELT LIKE IT.
[MINORI] WHOA! HEY,
BACK OFF! THAT HURTS!
[MARIELLE] YOU ARE JUST
ADORABLE, LIKE‐
ANYWAY, WE'RE DONE
GREETING EVERYBODY.
[MINORI] HUH?
(GIGGLING)
[MINORI] YEAH!
NOTHING BEATS THE BEACH!
[NAOTSUGU] CANNONBALL!
[TOYA] WHOO‐HOO!
(GIRLS SHRIEK)
DARN IT, TOYA!
THAT WAS ACTUALLY
A JACKKNIFE.
WHAT THE...?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING, RUNDELL?
[RUNDELLHAUS] EVERYONE,
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE FULLY
STRETCHED OUT FOR THE WATER?
IF YOU UNDERESTIMATE
THE SEA, BAD THINGS
CAN HAPPEN TO YOU.
[TOYA] (GARGLED)
TRANSLATION... RUNDELL
DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO SWIM.
[RUNDELLHAUS] PREPOSTEROUS!
HUH!
PEOPLE, LISTEN WELL.
MY BEAUTIFUL SWIMMING HAS BEEN
COMPARED TO THE LEAPING OF THE
MOST GRACEFUL DOLPHINS!
BEHOL‐ OHH!
DEAR GOD!
(RUNDELLHAUS SCREAMING)
[NYAN‐TA]
HERE YOU GO, BEAUTIFUL.
[MARIELLE] YOU'RE A GEM.
[MINORI] UM, MARIELLE, ABOUT
WHAT WE FOUND OUT EARLIER...
LATER, MINORI.
TIME FOR THE BEACH.
[MARIELLE] ENJOY YOURSELF
JUST LIKE I AM.
OHH.
NOW, AIN'T THAT
A SIGHT?
[KAYU]
BOSS, IT'S AWESOME!
SERIOUSLY! I MEAN,
LOOK AT THIS PLACE!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
ABOUT TWO HOURS FROM
THE CITY OF AKIHABARA
ON HORSEBACK AND COVERED
WAGON OR CAISSON,
WHERE SOUTHERN TOKYO WOULD
BE IN THE REAL WORLD,
WHERE HAMARIKYU PARK SITS,
IS THE PALACE OF ETERNAL ICE.
THIS MASSIVE AND COMPLEX
STRUCTURE IS A PALACE
WITH FOUNDATIONS CONSISTING OF
GIANT COLUMNS OF MAGICAL ICE
CREATED BY THE DEAD RACE
KNOWN AS THE ANCIENT ALVS.
(ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SHEEN)
[MICHITAKA]
THIS IS, UH, PRETTY.
[SHIROE]
I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD.
[KRUSTY]
JUST THINK OF EVERYONE AS A
BRIER WEASEL, THAT MIGHT HELP.
[MISA] I DON'T THINK
THAT PROCESS WORKS
FOR EVERYONE, MY LORD.
[AKATSUKI]
I REALLY LOOK AWKWARD.
[SHIROE] HUH?
UM, I MEAN,
I LOOK REALLY WEIRD.
RIGHT? DON'T I?
[SHIROE] HUH?
[HENRIETTA]
YOU DON'T LOOK WEIRD!
YOU LOOK ADORABLE
AND BEAUTIFUL,
LIKE SOME KIND OF FLUFFY
BLUEBERRY SOMETHING.
I JUST WANT TO
GOBBLE YOU UP...
MY LITTLE BLUEBERRY.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
OH, MY GOD, I WAS RIGHT.
SHE'S ONLY HERE
BECAUSE OF AKATSUKI.
[AKATSUKI] I JUST WANT
OUT OF THIS THING.
I DON'T DO DRESSES.
IT'S TOO HARD TO
CONCEAL MY WEAPONS.
(HENRIETTA GASPS)
WHOA. WHERE ON
EARTH WERE YOU
KEEPING THAT THING?
(MICHITAKA CHUCKLES)
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD!
[SHIROE] UH...
[KRUSTY] I GOT TO HAND
IT TO YOU, SHIROE.
YOUR COMPOSURE IS
INSPIRING US ALL.
BIG POLITICAL MASTERMIND
LIKE YOU? COME ON.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE A PROBLEM
ESCORTING TWO LOVELY LADIES
TO A SHINDIG LIKE THIS.
[HENRIETTA]
HOW RUDE.
A FANCY FORMAL SOCIAL
ENGAGEMENT LIKE THIS
IS NOTHING FOR
SINISTER SHIROE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
[SERJIAD] THANK YOU
FOR JOINING US TONIGHT.
(ROUND TABLE GASPS)
I AM DUKE SERJIAD COWEN.
AS THE DUKE OF MAIHAMA,
I AM THE RULER OF THE
CAPITAL OF EASTAL'S LEAGUE
OF FREEDOM CITIES.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
OH, WOW. HE'S A REAL NOBLEMAN.
[KRUSTY] YOU GRACE,
THANK YOU FOR INVITING US.
I AM KRUSTY, THE REPRESENTATIVE
FOR AKIHABARA'S ROUND
TABLE CONFERENCE.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
THAT WAS GUTSY.
KRUSTY EVEN LOOKS LIKE
A NOBLEMAN HIMSELF.
[SHIROE] OH! AND I
AM SHIROE, YOUR GRACE.
IT'S INDEED A
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
SERJIAD COWEN, LORD OF
THE LARGEST EASTERN CITY,
THE CAPITAL CITY
OF MAIHAMA,
EASILY THE MOST POWERFUL
PERSON IN EASTAL, LEAGUE
OF FREEDOM CITIES.
[SERJIAD] I SEE.
SO YOUR GUILDS ARE
LIKE NOBILITY,
BUT WITHOUT LAND OF
THEIR OWN TO RULE OVER.
AND I TAKE IT THE GUILDS
GUIDE POLICY THROUGH
DISCUSSION AND DEBATE.
THE STRUCTURE SEEMS COMPARABLE
TO THE WAY WE RUN EASTAL...
ON A SMALLER SCALE, OF COURSE.
[KRUSTY] CORRECT, YOUR GRACE.
[SERJIAD] WELL, THEN,
I'M ALREADY SEEING A PROBLEM
WITH OUR INITIAL OVERTURE
OF GRANTING A NOBLE TITLE
TO ONLY ONE GUILD MASTER,
IT WOULD CAUSE
NEEDLESS FRICTION.
[HENRIETTA]
OK, SHIROE.
AS EXPECTED, WE'RE ATTRACTING
A LOT OF ATTENTION TO OURSELVES.
WE'RE GETTING ATTENTION,
BUT NO ONE'S TALKING TO US.
[HENRIETTA] OUT OF
RESPECT FOR SERJIAD?
[SHIROE] NO.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
MORE THAN LIKELY, WE'RE GETTING
THE EXCLUSIVE EAR OF THE DUKE
BECAUSE INASMUCH AS
WE'RE CURIOUS ABOUT
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND,
THEY ARE EQUALLY AS CURIOUS
AND APPREHENSIVE ABOUT US.
THEY'RE NERVOUS, VERY NERVOUS.
THEY'RE PLAYING THE SAME
GAME WE ARE, ESSENTIALLY:
VERBAL FENCING,
ENGAGE US IN CONVERSATION
WITHOUT REVEALING TOO MUCH
ABOUT THEMSELVES IN THE PROCESS.
DODGE, WEAVE, PARRY.
THIS IS GONNA BE
A TOUGH NUT TO CRACK.
(MURMURING)
[MICHITAKA] WHOA.
[KAYU] HEY, I'VE NEVER SEEN
A REAL PRINCESS BEFORE.
[SERJIAD] THAT'S MY
GRANDDAUGHTER IN THE CENTER
WEARING THE LAVENDER.
[MICHITAKA]
AND SHE'S GORGEOUS.
[KRUSTY]
WHAT'S HER NAME?
[SERJIAD]
HMM. RAYNESHIA.
(BUGS CHIRPING)
[NAOTSUGU] AND TOMORROW
FOR GROUP TRAINING,
YOU'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO GO
INSIDE THE DUNGEON ITSELF.
[TOYA AND RUNDELLHAUS]
DUNGEON!
[NYAN‐TA] THIS PARTICULAR
DUNGEON IS CALLED
THE FOREST OF LAGLANDA.
[TOYA] ALL RIGHT!
[RUNDELLHAUS] YOU GUYS
ARE IN FOR A REAL TREAT.
[NAOTSUGU] BY THE WAY,
YOU'RE GONNA BE GOING IN
THERE WITHOUT US.
[TOYA] HUH?
(RUNDELLHAUS CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
[TOYA]
WITHOUT TRAINERS?
REALLY?
OH, SHIROE...
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
A BOUNTIFUL BANQUET CAN ALSO
BE A PLACE OF POLITICS
WHERE OPPOSING
GROUPS COLLIDE.
THE NOBLES TRY TO GAIN
CONTROL OF THE ADVENTURERS,
WHILE SHIROE AND
THE ROUND TABLE ARE
FORCED TO NEGOTIATE.
MEANWHILE, MINORI, TOYA,
AND THEIR COMPANIONS
FACE A HARSH REALITY.
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.