[PEPIN] UH.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
SUPPOSEDLY A MAN DIED
WHILE FIGHTING MONSTERS,
AND JUST LIKE IN THE GAME,
HE REVIVED IN THE CATHEDRAL.
[PEPIN] I'M ALIVE! I‐I TOTALLY
JUST CAME BACK TO LIFE!
[MAN 1] SERIOUSLY?
[MAN 2] WAIT, SO
DOESN'T THAT MEAN...
[PEPIN] I DIED,
AND I CAME BACK!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE MMORPG "ELDER TALES."
WITHOUT WARNING, AN ESTIMATED
30,000 JAPANESE PLAYERS,
AND SEVERAL HUNDRED
THOUSAND WORLDWIDE,
WERE TRAPPED IN A WORLD
THAT LOOKED JUST LIKE
THE ONE IN THAT GAME.
AND IN THIS WORLD,
DEATH IS NOT THE END.
WHOA!
ASTRAL BIND!
(TRIFFID GURGLES)
(PANT)
HUH!
[NAOTSUGU]
AND WE'RE DONE
WITH THAT.
[SHIROE] ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
LET'S CALL IT QUITS FOR TODAY.
YES, MY LORD.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE GOOD NEWS SEEMS TO BE
THAT OUR BODIES
ALREADY KNOW ALL THE
BASIC COMBAT MOVES...
AS IN WE DON'T
HAVE TO USE THE
GAME MENU TO FIGHT.
AS LONG AS WE HAVE
THE INTENT TO FIGHT
AND CAN SEE THE ENEMY
IN FRONT OF US,
WE CAN USE SKILLS
AND MAGIC AS IF WE
WERE USING VOICE INPUT.
HOWEVER, USING THE
SYSTEM AND MASTERING IT
ARE TWO DIFFERENT
THINGS ENTIRELY.
AND WE COULD USE
A LITTLE PRACTICE.
HOWEVER, I DON'T KNOW
IF PRACTICING THE WAY
MARTIAL ARTISTS DO IN OUR
WORLD WILL BE ENOUGH.
[AKATSUKI] LORD SHIROE?
[SHIROE] MISS AKATSUKI,
YOU KNOW YOU DON'T NEED TO
KEEP ON CALLING
ME THAT, OK?
"SHIROE" IS FINE.
WELL, THEN MAYBE YOU
SHOULD STOP REFERRING
TO ME AS "MISS."
[SHIROE] BUT...
THAT'S QUITE THE GAGGLE OF
LADIES YOU'RE BUILDING THERE.
DO ME A FAVOR AND SHUT
YOUR BIG DUMB FACE!
MY LORD.
[SHIROE] UH, YEAH?
[NAOTSUGU] HEH.
[AKATSUKI] I'D LIKE TO DO
SOME ADVANCE RECONNAISSANCE
ON THE WAY HOME, OK?
[SHIROE] AND WHY IS THAT?
[AKATSUKI] FOR PRACTICE.
ONE OF MY SKILLS AS AN
ASSASSIN IS DARK VISION.
I ALSO HAVE SNEAK AND
SILENT MOVE IN MY INVENTORY,
AND THE FOREST IS A
PERFECT PLACE TO PRACTICE.
[AKATSUKI]
I SHOULD TAKE ADVANTAGE.
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
[SHIROE] OK, LET'S MEET
UP AT THE SOUTH GATE.
I WILL ILLUMINATE THE PATH
WITH MAGIC LIGHT SO YOU
CAN SEE US ALONG THE WAY.
[AKATSUKI]
UNDERSTOOD.
[NAOTSUGU] SO AKATSUKI
HAS A SUBCLASS OF TRACKER
ON TOP OF BEING A NINJA?
[SHIROE] I DIDN'T EVEN HEAR
ANY LEAVES MOVING AROUND.
THAT GIRL IS PRETTY GOOD.
MAGIC LIGHT.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE SKILLS AKATSUKI MENTIONED,
SNEAK AND SILENT MOVE,
ARE TRACKER SKILLS.
TRACKER IS ONE
OF THE SUBCLASSES.
"ELDER TALES" HAS A
BUNCH OF SUBCLASSES
FOR AN ADVENTURER
TO CHOOSE FROM,
AFTER HE OR SHE HAS CHOSEN ONE
OF THE 12 MAIN COMBAT CLASSES.
MASTERING YOUR PRIMARY
AND SUBCLASS IS VITAL.
[NAOTSUGU] SO I GUESS ASSASSIN
AND TRACKER EQUALS NINJA.
REMIND ME NOT TO
PISS HER OFF.
[SHIROE] YOU ALREADY HAVE.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
YOU KNOW, I JUST REALIZED
I DON'T REMEMBER HOW LONG
WE'VE BEEN HERE.
[MARIELLE] PUBLIC ORDER
IN THE CITIES IS GOING
TO THE POOPER.
[SHIROE] YES.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE
RECRUITMENT RACE BETWEEN
THE GUILDS IS OVER,
SO WE CAN SAY ALL
THE LOCAL POWER
BASES ARE SET.
WE'LL SEE WHO
STARTS DOMINATING.
ADVENTURERS IN THE LARGER
GUILDS ARE SURE THROWING
THEIR WEIGHT AROUND.
AND THAT MEANS PEOPLE IN THE
SMALLER GUILDS ARE TRYING
TO STAY OUT OF SIGHT.
RIGHT. PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO
ACT LIKE YOU'RE AN ENEMY IF
YOU'RE NOT IN THEIR GUILD.
YEAH, BUT YOU CAN'T JUST
GO FIGHTING IN THE STREET,
NOW, CAN YOU?
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
FIGHTING WASN'T ALLOWED
IN THE MAJORITY OF TOWNS
WHEN ELDER TALES
WAS A GAME.
IF YOU TRIED TO
FIGHT IN A TOWN,
SPECIAL GUARDS CALLED THE
ROYAL GUARD WOULD APPEAR,
AND THAT WAS IT.
YOU RESISTED THE ROYAL GUARD,
YOU GOT SQUASHED AND REVIVED
IN THE CATHEDRAL.
[HIEN] AND THERE ARE STILL
WAYS TO HARASS SOMEONE
AND GET PHYSICAL WITH THEM
WITHOUT THE GUARD
SHOWING UP.
[EISEL] ON TOP OF THAT, PKs
HAVE BEEN ON THE RISE OVER
THE PAST FEW DAYS, TOO.
WHAT'S A PK?
PLAYER KILLINGS, OR AS SOME
PEOPLE SAY, PLAYER KILLER.
[HENRIETTA] THEY ATTACK
PLAYERS RATHER THAN MONSTERS,
THEN STEAL THE ITEMS AND MONEY
THEY DROP AFTER THEY DIE.
IT'S ABOUT THE WORST
THING YOU COULD DO.
[HIEN] MINIMAPS THAT TELL YOU
WHAT ELSE IS AROUND YOU
DON'T WORK OUTSIDE OF TOWN,
AND THERE'S NO ADMIN HERE.
[EISEL] BASICALLY, THERE
ARE PEOPLE TREATING
THIS AS A DEATH MATCH,
ENRICHING THEMSELVES
AT THE EXPENSE OF ANYONE
WHO ISN'T AS AGGRESSIVE.
AND ANYONE WHO'S ALREADY
DOING IT IS AHEAD OF THE
GAME AND THE OTHER GAMERS.
BUNCH OF JERKHOLES.
WELL, RIGHT NOW, FORTUNE
IS FAVORING THE "JERKHOLES."
[MARIELLE] HUH?
[SHIROE] HMM? WHAT'S
WRONG, MARIELLE?
(MARIELLE GASPS)
OH, IT'S NOTHING, REALLY!
I MEAN, ISN'T THIS JUST
A TERRIBLE SITUATION?
[MARIELLE]DON'T YOU
AGREE, NAOTSUGU?
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, GET OFF OF ME!
[NAOTSUGU] COME ON! AH! AH!
[HENRIETTA] OH, I WAS JUST SO
TAKEN BY AKATSUKI'S CUTENESS,
I FORGOT TO TAKE A BREATH
AND THINK CLEARLY ABOUT IT.
REALLY, I DID!
NYAH‐NYAH‐NYAH‐NYAH!
(HENRIETTA LAUGHS)
[NAOTSUGU] EARTH TO SHIROE.
[SHIROE] I'M HERE, I'M HERE.
YOU KNOW, SHIROE, I'VE BEEN
WATCHING YOU LATELY, MAN.
YEAH?
AND YOU NEED
TO LIGHTEN UP...
[NAOTSUGU] DUDE.
[SHIROE] YEAH, WHATEVER.
[NAOTSUGU]
HEY, SHORT STUFF!
[AKATSUKI] DON'T CALL
ME THAT, YOU BUTTFACE!
[NAOTSUGU] WERE THERE
ANY GOBLINS IN THERE?
[AKATSUKI] THERE WAS ONE
WITH A SKULL ON ITS HEAD.
WEIRD AND SILLY...
MY KIND OF GOBLIN.
[NAOTSUGU] UH, WHAT?
HUH?
[NAOTSUGU] I HEARD
SOMETHING, OR SOMEONE.
WE'VE GOT COMPANY.
HUH! WHOA!
OHH!
THANKS A LOT, SHIROE.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN QUICK TO
GET ME OUT OF A TIGHT SPOT.
SO WHAT'S THE
PLAN, MASTERMIND?
NAOTSUGU, TAKE UP
A TANDEM FORMATION.
WE'VE GOT PK'S OUT THERE,
AND I'VE GOT A VISUAL ON 4.
[SHIROE] GIVE ME A SEC.
GOT 'EM.
MIND BOLT!
[KATSUOMARU] HUH.
[SHIROE] THERE YOU GO.
OK, CREEPS, YOU GOT A LOT
OF GUTS TURNING INTO PKs.
HUH, MAYBE YOU SHOULD GET OUT
OF YOUR MOTHER'S BASEMENT
AND HAVE HER TEACH
YOU SOME MANNERS!
[SHIROE, THINKING] AT LEAST ONE
FIGHTER CLASS, TWO THIEVES,
ONE DRESSED LIKE A HEALER.
SO YOU CAN HAND OVER
EVERYTHING YOU HAVE
AND WE WON'T SEND YOUR SORRY
ASSES TO THE CATHEDRAL.
[SHIROE] FROM THE SOUND
OF IT, HE'S BEEN WATCHING
WAY TOO MUCH ANIME.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
HOWEVER, THEY'RE
HUMAN LIKE US.
[SHIROE]
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
KICK THEIR ASS!
I'M NOT BACKING
DOWN FROM FREAKS WHO
ATTACK PEOPLE FOR FUN!
[NAOTSUGU] YOU WANT TO TRY
THAT PK CRAP ON US,
THEN YOU SHOULD
PROBABLY GO BACK AND
GET SOME MORE GUYS!
[SHIROE]
I'D BE WILLING TO GIVE
THEM A COUPLE OF GOLD
IF IT WAS A ONE‐OFF
KIND OF DEAL.
(CHUCKLES)
THAT IS, IF THEY CAN BEAT US.
IT'S CLOBBERIN' TIME!
[SMASH] COME ON.
[SHIROE] THE WARRIOR IN FRONT
ON THE RIGHT, TARGET HIM FIRST.
KEEP THE OTHERS OCCUPIED
WHILE YOU'RE AT IT.
[NAOTSUGU] ROGER!
(GRUNTING)
[SMASH] I'VE GOT
THE FIGHTER. AH!
YOU ATTACK THE
MAGICAL NERD GUY.
[LYCOPENE] ROGER!
[SHIROE] ASTRAL BIND.
[LYCOPENE] AH!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] ASTRAL BIND
IS SIMPLY A SPELL THAT RESTRICTS
A TARGET'S MOVEMENTS.
IT KEEPS A TARGET FROM
COVERING LONG DISTANCES,
AND IT DOESN'T LAST LONG.
[SMASH] (GROANS)
FINE, I'LL TAKE THE MAGE.
YOU FIGHT THE STUPID WARRIOR.
I CAN TAKE CARE
OF THIS GUY.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
NORMALLY A GOOD CALL...
BUT NAOTSUGU ISN'T A SAMURAI;
HE'S A GUARDIAN.
ANCHOR HOWL!
(SMASH GROANS)
YOU SON OF A...
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
A GUARDIAN BELONGS TO A
LARGER GROUP CALLED TANKS,
AND A TANK PROTECTS THEIR
ALLIES BY INTERCEPTING ATTACKS.
ON TOP OF THAT, HE CAN
CAST THE ANCHOR HOWL.
THIS LITTLE SPELL KEEPS
ATTACKERS FROM IGNORING HIM.
IF THEY TRY ATTACKING
SOMEONE ELSE, THEY GET
CLOBBERED MAGICALLY.
[SMASH]
FINE! WHATEVER!
WE'LL BE HAPPY TO
KICK YOUR ASS FIRST.
YOU CAN'T BREAK
THIS ARMOR, D‐BAGS!
(GRUNTING)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] MAYBE,
BUT YOU'RE RUNNING OUT OF
HIT POINTS FAST THERE, BUDDY.
(NAOTSUGU GROANS)
[SHIROE]
ELECTRICAL FUZZ!
OOH!
[LYCOPENE] WAIT A SECOND.
HE'S AN ENCHANTER!
[KATSUOMARU] WHAT SPELL IS THAT?
IT DOESN'T HURT OR NOTHING.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] A MAGE
THAT IS ABLE TO CAST SPELLS
IS AN ENCHANTER.
IT'S ONE OF THE CLASSES
THAT USES OFFENSIVE MAGIC,
BUT ITS ATTACK POWER IS WEAK.
[LYCOPENE] AH!
[KATSUOMARU] HYAH!
[NAOTSUGU] UGH!
[SMASH] OH, SCARY.
WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO WITH
THAT SPELL ANYWAY?
[SHIROE] THORN BIND HOSTAGE.
AAH! HEY, WHAT
THE HELL, MAN?!
(GROANING)
YAA!
(KATSUOMARU SCREAMS)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THORN BIND HOSTAGE...
IT BINDS THE CASTER'S
TARGET IN SHINING THORNS,
AND FOR EVERY HIT AN ALLY IN
YOUR GROUP LANDS ON YOUR TARGET,
THE THORNS EXPLODE,
DEALING 1,000 DAMAGE.
(KATSUOMARU SCREAMS)
ULTIMATELY, ENCHANTERS
HAVE POOR OFFENSE,
BUT THEY CAN WEAKEN
AN ENEMY'S ATTACK,
OR INCREASE THE HEALTH
OF THEIR ALLIES.
YOU'RE GONNA LOSE HALF
THOSE HIT POINTS WHEN
THOSE VINES BLOW UP.
YOU WIENERS FEEL
LIKE GIVING UP?
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT!
[SMASH] WE NEED MORE
HIT POINTS. HEALER!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
ENCHANTERS ARE
PRETTY HELPLESS,
AND I DEFINITELY CAN'T
DO MUCH WITHOUT BACKUP.
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
IT'S A ROLE I LIKE.
[LYCOPENE]
TAKE THIS, DIRT BAG!
HA HA HA!
NOT VERY SMART FORMING A
PARTY WITHOUT A HEALER.
HAVE FUN CRYING IN THE
CATHEDRAL, JACKHOLES!
(KATSUOMARU SCREAMS)
UH!
[SMASH] HEALER, WE NEED
HEALTH OVER HERE!
HEY!
[SHIROE] I JUST CAST A SLEEP
ENCHANTMENT ON YOUR HEALER,
BUT HONESTLY, HE'S BEEN ASLEEP
SINCE WE STARTED THE FIGHT.
(SMASH GROANS)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
ASTRAL HYPNOS,
A STOP‐TARGET SPELL
THAT PUTS THE TARGET TO SLEEP.
[LYCOPENE]
THAT'S ENOUGH, FOUR‐EYES!
[SMASH]
NO, DON'T! NOT YET!
MY ANCHOR HOWL
HASN'T WORN OFF YET!
OH, GOD.
(LYCOPENE SCREAMS)
[SMASH] SCREW THIS!
SORCERER, SUMMONER,
LET'S KILL THESE CLOWNS
AND CALL IT A NIGHT ALREADY!
WE CAN'T LOSE TO A BUNCH
OF FREAKING DORKS!
(CHUCKLES)
UHH...
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE COVERT KILLER, ASSASSIN.
CLANDESTINE OPERATIONS
ARE THIS CLASS' SPECIALTY,
MAKING FOR QUICK
KILLS OUT OF SIGHT
AND OCCASIONALLY OUT OF MIND.
THE ANCHOR HOWL ATTRACTED
THE 4 PKs I SAW TO NAOTSUGU,
BUT THE 4 FRONTMEN DIDN'T
HAVE A SPELLCASTER.
WHEN I SAID I HAD A VISUAL ON 4,
AKATSUKI UNDERSTOOD
WHAT I MEANT
AND WENT OUT AHEAD OF US
TO NEUTRALIZE EVERYONE ELSE
WHO WAS HIDING IN THE FOREST.
YOU WERE NOT WISE TO INSULT
MY LORD'S MAGICAL ABILITIES.
YOU FOUND THE ELECTRICAL
FUZZ LAUGHABLE,
BUT ALL THOSE BRIGHT LIGHTS
KEPT YOU FROM SEEING
IN THE DARK FOREST.
YOU NEVER EVEN KNEW
YOUR HEALER WAS ASLEEP.
YOUR TEAMWORK IS NONEXISTENT.
[LYCOPENE]
AH! UH!
[AKATSUKI] YOUR LEADERSHIP
IS JUST PATHETIC.
YOU RUN YOUR MOUTH,
AND ALL THE WHILE
YOU AND THE REST OF YOUR PARTY
ARE LOSING HIT POINTS.
TAKING OUT YOUR AMBUSH
PARTY WAS EASY.
[SMASH] SHUT UP!
KILLING US WON'T
CHANGE ANYTHING.
WE'LL JUST COME BACK
AND GET YOU AGAIN.
[AKATSUKI]
YOU WANT TO TRY IT?
(SMASH COWERS)
[SMASH] I'M SORRY.
I WON'T DO IT AGAIN.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
I'M BEGGING YOU!
(VOICE CRACKING)
I'M SORRY.
(WHISPERING)
NOT SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU FELL FOR THAT!
AH... UH‐OH.
(FUMING)
[AKATSUKI] PUBLIC SAFETY REALLY
IS GETTING BAD, ISN'T IT?
[SHIROE] IT'S NOT LIKE
THERE'S A LOT TO BE GAINED
BY PLAYER‐KILLING.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
WE'RE ALL IN THE SAME
BOAT RIGHT NOW.
SO WHY DON'T THESE GUYS
JUST FIND OTHER THINGS
TO OCCUPY THEIR TIME WITH?
[AKATSUKI] LIKE WHAT?
[NAOTSUGU]
I KNOW WHAT I‐ OWW!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, MAY I
TAKE A MOMENT AND KNEE THIS
RIDICULOUS PERVERT IN THE FACE?
[NAOTSUGU] ASK BEFORE YOU DO IT,
AND LET ME FINISH MY SENTENCE!
[AKATSUKI] I DIDN'T WANT YOU
TO SAY SOMETHING THAT WOULD
GET YOU IN TROUBLE.
[NAOTSUGU] THAT DOESN'T
EVEN MAKE SENSE!
[SHIROE]
OTHER THINGS TO DO?
THAT MIGHT BE IT.
THERE REALLY IS NOTHING.
THERE REALLY ARE NO GOALS.
[SHIROE] IT'S NOT MUCH,
BUT THERE IS FOOD TO BE HAD.
YOU CAN MAKE THE MONEY FOR
THAT AND A PLACE TO STAY
BY DESTROYING LOW‐LEVEL
MONSTERS, I GUESS.
I MEAN, NOTHING IS
ALL THAT EXPENSIVE.
FIGHTING ISN'T ALLOWED IN TOWN,
SO YOU'RE PRETTY SAFE.
AND DEATH ISN'T EVEN PERMANENT.
[NAOTSUGU] SO BASICALLY
YOU'RE SAYING YOU CAN
SURVIVE IN THIS WORLD
WITHOUT REALLY
DOING ANYTHING?
[SHIROE]
PRETTY MUCH, BUT IT'S
NOT MY IDEA OF LIVING.
OR IS IT STAYING ALIVE?
SO THEY'VE RESORTED TO KILLING
OTHER PLAYERS BECAUSE THERE'S
NOTHING ELSE TO DO?
[SHIROE]
I GUESS SO.
THEY'RE BORED,
THERE AREN'T ANY JOBS
HERE REALLY, SO, YEAH.
[NAOTSUGU] OK, SO THEY
WANT TO GET THEIR ROCKS
OFF BY HURTING OTHER PEOPLE?
THAT'S STUPID.
[SHIROE] PRETTY LAME,
AND DEFINITELY MESSED UP.
SICK, REALLY.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
THING IS, IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M DOING ANYTHING EITHER.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD?
[SHIROE] HUH?
UH, ANYWAY, I'M NOT
REALLY SURE IF THINGS
ARE GETTING WORSE, SO FAR.
HMM.
[SHIROE] IT JUST SEEMS THAT WAY,
AND IT PROBABLY HAS TO DO
WITH THE FACT THAT PEOPLE STILL
THINK THAT THIS IS A GAME WORLD
WITHOUT ANY REAL
PENALTIES TO SPEAK OF.
IF THIS IS A DIFFERENT WORLD,
THEN MAYBE OUR SENSE
OF PUBLIC ORDER
IS REALLY AN ILLUSION.
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD...
(RINGING)
UH... YES?
[AKATSUKI] HUH?
[SHIROE] HUH?
[NAOTSUGU] YOU'RE
GOING TO SUSUKINO?
[HENRIETTA] ON THE DAY
OF THE APOCALYPSE,
ONE OF OUR MEMBERS
WAS GOING TO SUSUKINO.
[MARIELLE] SHE'S A YOUNGER
GIRL NAMED SERARA.
[SHIROE] YOU'RE
GOING TO FIND HER?
[NAOTSUGU] AREN'T THE INTERCITY
TRANSPORT GATES STILL DOWN?
FAIRY RINGS ARE THE ONLY
OTHER WAY TO GET THERE
IF YOU HAVE THEM.
[NAOTSUGU]
NOT ME.
RIGHT, BUT WITHOUT
THE ONLINE HELP
OR SOMEONE WHO'S MEMORIZED
THE TIMETABLES,
YOU COULD END UP
TRANSPORTED INTO THE
MIDDLE OF WHO KNOWS WHERE
WITH THOSE FAIRY RINGS.
OK, WHY NOT TRY THE RETURN
SPELL "CALL TO HOME"?
DOESN'T LET YOU
RETURN TO THE LAST
5 GREAT CITIES...
OH, CRAP.
[HENRIETTA] MM‐HMM.
AND THE LAST GREAT CITY
SHE VISITED WAS SUSUKINO.
[NAOTSUGU] LIKE I
SAID, OH, CRAP.
[SHIROE] SO THAT LEAVES
WALKING AND HORSEBACK.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IN THE REAL WORLD,
THERE ARE 850 KILOMETERS
BETWEEN TOKYO AND SAPPORO.
THE "ELDER TALES" WORLD
IS HALF‐SCALE, SO IT
WOULD BE 425 KILOMETERS.
AND NATURALLY, THEY'RE
GOING TO RUN INTO PACKS
OF MONSTERS OUT THERE.
[SHIROE] SO WHY ARE YOU
SENDING HELP NOW?
HUH? OH, UM...
[HENRIETTA] WE'VE BEEN
PLANNING TO SEND A RESCUE
TEAM FOR A WHILE NOW.
MARIELLE?
AH, DON'T LOOK
AT ME THAT WAY!
YOUR EYES ARE LIKE DAGGERS,
AND YOU KNOW A GIRL
DOESN'T LIKE A GUY WHO
STARES AT HER LIKE THAT!
(MARIELLE COWERS)
(MARIELLE SIGHS)
HERE'S THE THING:
THE PUBLIC SAFETY
ISSUE'S A LOT WORSE
IN SUSUKINO THAN HERE.
[HENRIETTA]
MARIELLE...
[MARIELLE] SOME NASTY...
AND I MEAN REALLY NASTY
PEOPLE ATTACKED
ONE OF OUR FRIENDS.
LUCKILY, SOMEBODY JUMPED
IN AND SAVED HER.
[HENRIETTA] AND NOW
HE'S PROTECTING HER.
[MARIELLE] ANYWAY, WE'RE
GETTING READY TO TAKE
OUR MOST POWERFUL PEOPLE
TO SUSUKINO TO BRING HER BACK.
SO I THOUGHT... I WAS
THINKING THAT MAYBE...
COULD YOU WATCH OVER
THE REST OF OUR GUILD?
[HENRIETTA] CAN YOU
DO THIS FOR US?
[MARIELLE]
WE'RE TOTALLY
BEGGING YOU.
[SHIROE, THINKING] I DOUBT
THEY CAN GET TO SUSUKINO
ANY FASTER THAN 21 DAYS...
MORE THAN A MONTH, PROBABLY,
TWO FOR THE ROUND TRIP.
EVEN IF THEY TAKE THE
CRESCENT MOON'S MOST
POWERFUL PLAYERS, IT'S DICEY.
AND ON TOP OF THAT,
THE GAME ONLY ALLOWS
A MAXIMUM PARTY SIZE OF 6,
AND EVEN THE BEST 6 DON'T HAVE
A GOOD HEALER AMONG THEM.
NO, IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
THEIR PARTY STILL WON'T MAKE IT.
SO WHAT DO THEY DO?
WE'RE STRONG ENOUGH.
WE SHOULD GO.
WE SHOULD, BUT WE ALSO
SHOULDN'T STICK OUR NOSE
IN SOME GUILD'S BUSINESS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THEY WOULDN'T WANT THAT,
AND I WOULDN'T BLAME THEM.
SHOULDN'T I AT LEAST...
SHOULDN'T I...
(THUD)
[SHIROE] HUH?
SAY IT, SHIROE.
YOU WERE ABOUT
TO SAY SOMETHING?
(SHIROE SIGHS)
[SHIROE]
WE'LL BRING HER BACK.
(HENRIETTA AND MARIELLE GASP)
WE HAVE THE BEST
CHANCE TO GET HER.
[HENRIETTA AND MARIELLE] OHH.
[HENRIETTA] SHIROE,
NAOTSUGU, AKATSUKI...
[MARIELLE]
... BRING HER BACK TO US.
[AKATSUKI]
DON'T WORRY, MARIELLE.
YOU CAN COUNT ON US.
WE'LL SEE THIS THING
THROUGH. WE DON'T KNOW
THE MEANING OF FAILURE.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] JUST LIKE
IN THE GAME, WE WERE ABLE
TO USE ITEMS TO SUMMON HORSES.
(FLUTES BLOWING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
[NAOTSUGU] HUH!
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, WHERE
DO YOU THINK THESE
HORSES COME FROM ANYWAY?
[SHIROE] THIS IS COOL.
WE ALREADY KNOW
HOW TO RIDE THEM, TOO.
(GROANING)
(BONES CRACKING)
[NAOTSUGU] I LIKE THE FACT
THAT I ALREADY KNOW
HOW TO RIDE A HORSE,
BUT IT DOESN'T HURT
MY ASS ANY LESS.
[AKATSUKI] YOU DESERVE IT.
[NAOTSUGU] YOU SMELL.
[AKATSUKI] THAT'S A REALLY NICE
MAP YOU HAVE THERE, MY LORD.
OH, I WANTED MY SUBCLASS TO
BE SCRIBE WHEN I SIGNED UP.
I MADE A COPY OF THE MAPS I
SAW OVER AT THE CITY ARCHIVES.
[AKATSUKI]
INTERESTING.
VERY WELL DONE.
[NAOTSUGU]
OK, SO WHERE THE
HECK ARE WE NOW?
[SHIROE]
WORKING ON IT.
[NAOTSUGU] SERIOUSLY?
WE ARE FREAKING LOST.
[SHIROE] DON'T WORRY.
I'M GONNA GET US THERE.
[NAOTSUGU AND AKATSUKI] ROGER.
[NAOTSUGU] MAN, I WISH YOU COULD
MAGIC UP A WAY TO MAKE THIS FOOD
NOT TASTE LIKE DOOKIE.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
WE'LL BRING HER BACK.
(SHIROE SIGHS)
[NAOTSUGU] IF SOMEONE YOU
KNOW IS CRYING, YOU HELP.
[SHIROE] UH.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE
DOING THIS, RIGHT?
[AKATSUKI] YES.
THERE MIGHT
NOT BE ANY JOBS,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU CAN RUN AROUND BEING
A TOTAL FARTKNOCKER.
I DEFINITELY AGREE.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THIS IS MY... OUR ANSWER.
THIS IS WHAT WE CAN DO.
[NAOTSUGU] OR ARE WE
TOO COOL FOR THAT?
[SHIROE] HEH. NO.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
BUT, YOU KNOW,
I'D PUT IT RIGHT UP THERE
WITH THE COOLNESS LEVEL
OF OUR OLD DEBAUCHERY
TEA PARTY...
IF THERE'S SUCH A THING
AS A COOLNESS LEVEL.
[NAOTSUGU]
ALL RIGHT.
[SHIROE] HANG ON.
[AKATSUKI] WHAT
ARE THOSE, MY LORD?
[NAOTSUGU] HEH?
(BOTH PLAY FLUTES)
(SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
[AKATSUKI]
THOSE ARE GRIFFINS!
YEAH, OF COURSE
THEY ARE.
[NAOTSUGU] SERIOUSLY,
WE WEREN'T GONNA GO
THAT FAR NORTH TO SUSUKINO
ON HORSEBACK, YOU KNOW.
[AKATSUKI]
BUT THEY'RE... MONSTERS.
[NAOTSUGU] GIVE ME FIVE, BEAKY.
(AKATSUKI GASPS)
[AKATSUKI] WAIT,
THOSE ARE OUR MOUNTS?
[NAOTSUGU] OW!
[SHIROE] YES, THEY ARE,
MISS AKATSUKI.
JUST "AKATSUKI."
[SHIROE] OK, "AKATSUKI."
RIDE BEHIND ME, OK?
[AKATSUKI] UH, ALL RIGHT.
(GRIFFIN SCREECHES)
[AKATSUKI]
UH! EASY, BOY.
(NAOTSUGU GRUNTS)
(SCREECHING)
[AKATSUKI] I'VE HEARD
OF THOSE SUMMONING
FLUTES, YOU KNOW.
THEY WERE ITEMS GIVEN
ONLY TO CERTAIN PLAYERS,
THOSE WHO WON THE
HADES BREATH RAID MISSION
ON THE FIELDS OF DEATH.
DID YOU PLAY
THAT ONE?
[SHIROE] OH, YEAH.
A WHILE BACK.
[NAOTSUGU] WAIT TILL
YOU SEE THE STUPID
LOOK ON PEOPLE'S FACES
WHEN THEY SEE THESE.
UHH...
[SHIROE]
COME ON, AKATSUKI.
(GRIFFIN SCREECHES)
UH!
(AKATSUKI SHUDDERS)
[SHIROE] HMM?
ALL RIGHT,
READY TO GET GOING?
YES, MY LORD.
NO PROBLEM.
I CAN DO THIS.
[SHIROE]
OK. HANG ON TIGHT.
[NAOTSUGU]
EASY. EASY,
YOU BIG GOOF!
OH‐HO‐HO!
I'M UP FIRST!
YAHOO!
COME ON, LOSERS!
(GRIFFIN SCREECHES)
[SHIROE] JEEZ.
OK, AKATSUKI.
LET'S GET MOVING.
(CRINGING)
(GRIFFINS SCREECHES)
[SHIROE]
IT'S A GREAT VIEW.
(AKATSUKI GASPS)
[SHIROE]
ARE YOU OK?
[AKATSUKI] YEAH...
MY LORD,
THIS IS AMAZING.
[AKATSUKI] I'VE NEVER DONE
ANYTHING LIKE THIS BEFORE!
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH,
IT'S GREAT, RIGHT?!
[AKATSUKI]
OH, MY GOD, IT'S AWESOME!
THE SKY AND ALL THE CLOUDS...
THEY'RE SO BEAUTIFUL.
UH... HMM.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
SHIROE'S PARTY TRAVELS THROUGH
AN UNDERGROUND LABYRINTH
ON THE WAY TO SUSUKINO.
AWAITING THEM ARE PHANTOMS
OF THE PAST AND A HORDE OF
DEMI‐HUMANS CALLED THE RAT‐MEN,
AND IT TURNS OUT,
SHIROE ONCE HAD A GROUP OF
FRIENDS HE HELD VERY DEAR.
THEY WERE KNOWN AS
THE DEBAUCHERY TEA PARTY.
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.