[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] NON‐PLAYER
CHARACTERS ARE PEOPLE IN THE
GAME THAT AREN'T PLAYERS.
THEIR DIALOGUE IS SET
BY THE PROGRAMMERS,
AND THEY DON'T HAVE
DISTINCT PERSONALITIES.
THEY'RE PRETTY MUCH THERE TO
FULFILL ROLES AT CERTAIN
POINTS IN THE GAME.
IN "ELDER TALES," PLAYERS
ARE CALLED ADVENTURERS,
AND NON‐PLAYERS ARE CALLED
PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
HOWEVER, THE APOCALYPSE
MAY HAVE CHANGED THAT.
[MARIELLE] SERARA?
YOU'RE OK, RIGHT?
I‐I'M, LIKE, SO GLAD
YOU MADE IT BACK
FROM SUSUKINO, SWEETIE!
[SERARA] YES. I'M SORRY
I WORRIED YOU.
GOOD‐BYE.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I'M REALLY SAFE NOW, RIGHT?
[SHIROE] YEAH. WE'RE PAST
THE LYPORT CHANNEL NOW.
[NYAN‐TA] AND BRIGANDIA
DOESN'T HAVE ANY GRIFFINS.
THEY'RE WEEKS BEHIND US,
SO DON'T EVEN WORRY.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
UH...
[SERARA] NOW THAT I'M SAFE,
I JUST FEEL KIND OF...
THANK YOU, EVERYONE!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
(STOMACH GROWLS)
UH!
UH‐OH. LOOKS LIKE
SOMEBODY'S TUM‐TUM
ISN'T TOO HAPPY.
[AKATSUKI] DO YOU
EVER SHUT UP?!
[NAOTSUGU]
HEY, I FART, TOO.
(LAUGHTER)
[NAOTSUGU] OH, MAN.
YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER
PITCHED A TENT BEFORE.
[SHIROE]
WELL, START BY LAYING
OUT THE GROUND SHEETS.
UH, I DON'T REMEMBER
YOU SAYING YOU EVER
ROUGHED IT BACK HOME.
THAT'S TRUE, BUT I READ
A BOOK ABOUT IT ONCE.
OF COURSE, I'M BETTING
IT PROBABLY WOULDN'T BE
THIS EASY FOR ME
IN THE REAL WORLD.
YEAH, I GUESS THAT'S
TRUE ABOUT A LOT OF
THINGS AROUND HERE.
[NAOTSUGU]
IT'S PRETTY CRAZY.
(RUSTLING)
(GASPS)
[SERARA]
WILD DEER?
SO THERE ARE ANIMALS IN THIS
GAME THAT AREN'T MONSTERS.
[NYAN‐TA]
WELL, NOW.
THIS IS WHAT I CALL
A TIME TO SHINE.
(DING)
[SERARA] AH!
[NAOTSUGU]
THERE WE GO.
WE'VE GOT A
PLACE TO SLEEP.
[SHIROE] IT'S KIND OF
SATISFYING, COMPARED TO JUST
HAVING TO LOG OUT AND GO TO BED.
[NAOTSUGU] SINCE WE'RE OUT IN
THE BUSH, WE MIGHT AS WELL HAVE
FUN DOING IT THE HARD WAY.
[SHIROE]
THAT'S RIGHT.
[SHIROE] BUT OUR FOOD
ISN'T EXACTLY...
[NAOTSUGU] IT LOOKS
SO GOOD, SHIROE,
BUT IT STILL TASTES LIKE
ABSOLUTE GARBAGE!
[AKATSUKI] SERARA AND
NYAN‐TA ARE RUNNING LATE.
(NAOTSUGU SNIFFS)
DO YOU SMELL THAT?!
[SHIROE]
WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO YOU?
(NAOTSUGU AND AKATSUKI SNIFF)
WHAT?
IT SMELLS LIKE
MEAT ROASTING.
(SIZZLING)
[NYAN‐TA] HMM, DID THE SMELL
OF THIS FINE CUISINE ROUSE YOU
FROM YOUR BASE CAMP?
[SERARA] HEY!
[NAOTSUGU] TELL YOU WHAT,
I'M WILLING TO GIVE
TASTELESS MEAT A TRY
IF IT SMELLS THIS GOOD.
(TRIUMPHANT BELLS)
YEAH!
(MOUTH FULL)
THIS IS...
I CAN'T DESCRIBE IT!
[SHIROE] (MOUTH FULL)
THE TEXTURE WHEN
YOU BITE INTO IT...
THE DELICIOUS JUICES!
[NAOTSUGU] THE SWEETNESS
OF THE FAT... AWESOME!
(MOUTH FULL)
JUST THE RIGHT
AMOUNT OF SALT,
AND HE OBVIOUSLY USED
ROSEMARY IN IT, TOO!
IT'S, WITHOUT A DOUBT...
[ALL] REAL FREAKING FOOD!
[NYAN‐TA] OH, YEAH.
AWESOME! I LOVE YOU!
MORE, PLEASE!
[NYAN‐TA] NOW, NOW.
[SHIROE, AKATSUKI, AND NAOTSUGU]
PLEASE, PLEASE!
[NYAN‐TA]
PLENTY TO GO AROUND.
SO, HOW THE HECK
DID YOU DO IT ANYWAY?
(SERARA GIGGLES)
WELL, AS YOU KNOW,
YOU CAN PICK THE ITEM YOU
WANT FROM OFF THE MENU.
YOU DIG?
AND IT WILL MAKE
YOU FOOD ITEMS
THAT LOOK JUST LIKE
THE REAL THING.
[SHIROE]
RIGHT. THAT'S JUST
LIKE THE GAME.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, BUT
YOUR FOOD HAS FLAVOR.
[NYAN‐TA] AND THAT'S EXACTLY
WHY YOU NEED TO STOP THINKING
OF THIS AS A GAME.
AFTER ALL, FRUITS AND VEGETABLES
STILL HAVE THEIR FLAVOR, RIGHT?
[NAOTSUGU] HUH.
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
WELL, THEN.
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS
THE SAME THING I DID:
JUST DON'T USE
THE INTERFACE.
FORGET ABOUT TAPPING
YOUR FINGERS IN THE AIR
AND USE YOUR OWN HANDS
TO COOK YOUR DINNER.
IT'S THAT EASY, BABY.
I KNOW. I TRIED TO
DO THAT, TOO, CHIEF.
CHECK IT OUT.
[NAOTSUGU]
BLAM‐O!
PURPLE PUKE STICK!
[SHIROE] BOILING IT TURNS IT
INTO A WEIRD PASTE OF SOME KIND.
NO MATTER WHAT WE DO,
IT ALL TURNS OUT LIKE THIS.
I MEAN, WE JUST FIGURED
THAT THIS WAS THE WAY
IT WAS GONNA BE HERE.
[NYAN‐TA] WELL, IT SOUNDS TO ME
AS IF THE PERSON WHO WAS
PREPARING YOUR FOOD
DIDN'T HAVE A SUBCLASS OF CHEF
OR OTHER SIMILAR COOKING SKILL.
[NAOTSUGU]
OK. SO YOU'RE...
THAT'S RIGHT, HOLMES.
I HAVE MASTERED THE GENTLEMANLY
ART OF BEING A CHEF.
[NAOTSUGU] WHOA.
[SHIROE] MAKES SENSE.
SO SOMEONE HAS TO HAVE
THE SKILL AHEAD OF TIME
TO MAKE A DECENT
MEAL FOR HIMSELF.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
HE'S GOT A POINT.
I'M REALLY STILL STUCK
IN THAT GAMER MENTALITY,
WHICH MEANS...
(NAOTSUGU CHEWS LOUDLY)
[AKATSUKI] MASTER NYAN‐TA?
[NAOTSUGU] "MASTER"? REALLY?
[AKATSUKI] ALLOW ME TO
INTRODUCE MYSELF PROPERLY.
MY NAME IS AKATSUKI.
MY CLASS IS ASSASSIN,
AND I'M AT LEVEL 90.
[NYAN‐TA] AND YOU DID SOME FINE
WORK BACK THERE, YOUNG LADY.
[AKATSUKI] IT WAS NOTHING.
THE WAY YOU FOUGHT
WAS MASTERFUL.
[NAOTSUGU]
WELL, HOLD UP. I HAD A
PRETTY GOOD FIGHT MYSELF.
YOU ARE A
WORTHLESS TURD.
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
[AKATSUKI] WHATEVER, TURD.
[NAOTSUGU] YOU'RE A TURD.
(SHIROE AND NYAN‐TA CHUCKLE)
[NYAN‐TA] I SEE YOU HAVE
SOME GOOD COMPANIONS...
YOU, TOO,
LITTLE ONE.
HUH! RIGHT!
I GUESS I SHOULD INTRODUCE
MYSELF PROPERLY.
I'M SERARA WITH THE CRESCENT
MOON ALLIANCE GUILD.
I'M A LEVEL 19 DRUID,
AND MY SUBCLASS IS MAID,
AND I... AND I GUESS THAT'S ALL.
BUT, UH, I...
[SERARA]
I'M SORRY FOR THE
TROUBLE I CAUSED WITH
MY POOR HEALING SKILLS
BACK IN SUSUKINO.
[NAOTSUGU] DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, OK?
[SHIROE] HMM.
THANK YOU FOR
YOUR KIND WORDS,
AND THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HELP, SHIROE.
HUH?
[SERARA] IT REALLY
MEANS SO MUCH TO ME,
I CAN'T TELL YOU!
[SHIROE] UH, NO.
I REALLY DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING THAT WAS ALL
THAT SPECIAL, ALL RIGHT?
HUH?
MY BOY'S ALWAYS BEEN
THE KIND OF FELLA WHO'S
EASY TO EMBARRASS.
I BET I KNOW
ALL ABOUT YOU.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN TOLD
YOU'RE THE THIRD‐CUTEST
IN YOUR CLASS,
AND YOU PROBABLY GOT
MORE SECRET LOVE LETTERS
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
[SERARA]
UH, YEAH.
(NAOTSUGU WAILS)
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD, I HAVE JUST GIVEN
NAOTSUGU A BLOODY NOSE.
[NAOTSUGU] I HAVE HAD JUST ABOUT
ENOUGH OF YOU AND YOUR LITTLE,
PAINFUL PROGRESS REPORTS!
[AKATSUKI]
I'VE ALSO DECIDED
TO EAT HIS DINNER.
AAH!
(CRACKLING)
(NAOTSUGU GROANS)
I CAN'T MOVE!
[AKATSUKI] YOU ATE
TOO MUCH, YOU DUMMY.
[SERARA]
NYAN‐TA, I GUESS YOU AND
MR. SHIROE HAVE KNOWN EACH OTHER
FOR A REALLY
LONG TIME, HUH?
[NYAN‐TA] DON'T FORGET
ABOUT NAOTSUGUCCHI.
BACK WHEN WE WERE
PLAYING THIS AS A GAME,
WE ALL JUST HAPPENED TO BE
IN THE SAME LOOSE‐KNIT
GROUP OF PLAYERS.
YOU MIGHT'VE EVEN
HEARD OF US...
WE WERE THE DEBAUCHERY
TEA PARTY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I'VE HEARD STORIES ABOUT A
LEGENDARY GROUP THAT COMPLETED
A LOT OF DIFFICULT QUESTS
WHEN THE ADMINS ADDED
THEM TO THE GAME.
[AKATSUKI] THAT WAS MY LORD
AND MASTER NYAN‐TA?
HEY, DON'T FORGET
ABOUT ME!
[SERARA] WOW. SO THAT MEANS
ALL OF YOU WERE IN THE SAME
GUILD TOGETHER ONCE.
[NAOTSUGU]
NAH, IT WASN'T A GUILD...
MORE LIKE A HANGOUT.
[SERARA] OH.
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF
US WAS IN A DIFFERENT
GUILD AT THE TIME.
AND WE WEREN'T
ALL THAT ORGANIZED,
BUT WE DID HAVE
SOME GOOD ADVENTURES
TOGETHER, YOU KNOW?
[NYAN‐TA] I SUPPOSE THAT'S
WHAT MADE US STRONG.
[NAOTSUGU] HMM.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
THAT EXPLAINS A LOT.
I GUESS I DON'T HAVE TO ASK
WHY MY LORD AND HIS FRIENDS
CAN SUMMON GRIFFINS.
THAT'S A HIGH‐LEVEL QUEST,
AND THAT'S HOW THEY WORK
SO WELL TOGETHER.
(AKATSUKI WINCES)
I FOUGHT BY MY LORD'S SIDE ON
SEVERAL DIFFERENT OCCASIONS NOW.
I'M NOT EVEN CLOSE TO WORKING
IN TANDEM WITH HIM LIKE THAT.
I HAVE TO PRACTICE MORE.
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI?
[NAOTSUGU] TUMMY ACHE?
[AKATSUKI] SHUT. UP.
NOW, THEN, IT'S OBVIOUS
YOU JUST LIED TO ME.
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
THERE'S NO WAY THE
DEBAUCHERY TEA PARTY
COULD'VE HAD SOMEONE
LIKE NAOTSUGU IN IT.
I WAS THERE!
(CRACKLING)
[NYAN‐TA] WHEN ALL
WAS SAID AND DONE,
WE'D GONE ON QUITE
A FEW QUESTS
AND SEEN QUITE A
FEW PLACES, HMM?
[NAOTSUGU]
MADE FRIENDS,
DID QUESTS...
IT WAS A
BLAST, DUDE.
RIGHT.
(GRIFFINS SCREECH)
[NYAN‐TA] MMM.
[SERARA, THINKING]
NYAN‐TA IS SO AWESOME!
HE'S HANDSOME, YOUNG, KIND,
AND ALWAYS WILLING TO HELP.
NO, I THINK HE'S OLDER.
A HANDSOME MIDDLE‐AGED
MAN? BUT HE'S SO IN SHAPE.
SERIOUSLY, I WONDER
HOW HE DOES IT.
NEXT TO HIM, I LOOK KIND OF FAT.
OK, MAYBE I'M A
LITTLE OVERWEIGHT...
[SERARA] OH, NYAN‐TA,
YOU'RE JUST SO PERFECT...
[NAOTSUGU] SO OBVIOUS.
SO THE LITTLE GINGER'S
INTO OLDER CAT DUDES.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
I GUESS NYAN‐TA'S
GOT IT GOING ON.
(SHIROE CHUCKLES)
SERARA HAS
GOOD TASTE.
[BOTH] HUH?!
[SHIROE] YOU MEAN YOU'VE GOT
A THING FOR CAT GUYS, TOO?!
[NYAN‐TA] MEOW?
[AKATSUKI] THE MASTER IS
A FIRST‐CLASS SWORDSMAN.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
OK. SWORDSMAN. HMM.
I WONDER IF THE CHIEF'S OK
WITH ALL THEIR GIRLIE STUFF.
[AKATSUKI] UM, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] HMM?
YOU MAY NOT BE ADEPT
WITH A SWORD OR ANYTHING,
BUT YOU DO HAVE OTHER
APPRECIABLE TALENTS.
UH, OH, YEAH?
YOU DIDN'T THINK YOU HURT MY
FEELINGS OR SOMETHING, DID YOU?
UH... UH...
OF COURSE NOT.
[SHIROE] HMM?
[NAOTSUGU] WHEN YOU SEE HER
LIKE THIS, SHE REALLY DOES
LOOK KIND OF YOUNG.
[SHIROE] HOW OLD DO YOU
THINK SHE REALLY IS?
[NAOTSUGU] WHO KNOWS?
I MEAN, WE ALL LOOK LIKE
OUR GAME AVATARS HERE.
JUST BASED ON HER LOOKS,
I'D SAY THAT SHE WAS
IN ELEMENTARY‐
OHH! GOD!
[SHIROE]
MIDDLE SCHOOLER, MAYBE?
I WONDER.
I GUESS SHE'D BE THE
SAME AGE AS THE TWINS.
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT TWINS?
[SHIROE] I RAN INTO THEM WHEN
THIS WAS STILL JUST A GAME.
THE GIRL WAS A SHRINE MAIDEN,
AND HER TWIN BROTHER
WAS A SAMURAI.
[BOY] MISTER?
MISTER! HEY, STOP!
[GIRL] UM, CAN WE
ASK YOU SOMETHING?
[BOY] A QUESTION!
[GIRL] MY BROTHER WAS JUST
IN A REALLY BIG FIGHT
AND I'M TRYING TO
HEAL HIS WOUNDS,
BUT MY MAGIC
IS TOO WEAK.
DO YOU KNOW WHERE I CAN BUY
ALL THE MAGIC‐Y STUFF?
[BOY] I NEED SKILLS,
TOO, DUDE. CAN YOU TELL
US WHERE TO GET 'EM?
[SHIROE] SO I'M GUESSING
THIS IS YOUR FIRST
TIME TO PLAY, HUH?
[GIRL] YEAH.
[BOY] THAT'S RIGHT.
[NAOTSUGU] REALLY? HAVE YOU
ALWAYS BEEN THAT NICE?
[SHIROE] I USUALLY DON'T LIKE
IT WHEN PEOPLE RUN UP ON ME
FOR ADVICE LIKE THAT.
[NYAN‐TA] TRUE.
[SHIROE] IT WAS THEIR FIRST
DAY PLAYING, YOU KNOW,
AND IT SEEMED LIKE THEY WERE
ADVENTURING JUST FOR THE
SAKE OF ADVENTURE.
I EVEN TOOK SOME TIME
OFF FROM MY QUEST TO
SHOW THEM AROUND.
THE TEACHER SYSTEM
REALLY HELPED A LOT.
[AKATSUKI]
"TEACHER SYSTEM"?
[SHIROE] A SYSTEM THAT
ALLOWS HIGH‐LEVEL PLAYERS
TO DECREASE THEIR ABILITY
SO THAT THEY CAN PLAY WITH
THE LOWER‐LEVEL CHARACTERS.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, BUT
HARDLY ANYONE USED IT.
IT WAS TOO RISKY.
YEAH, WELL, THAT WAS THE
IDEA BEHIND IT, THOUGH.
YOU COULD REENACT HOW YOU
PLAYED AT THE BEGINNING.
SO THE PEOPLE YOU
WERE TEACHING WOULD
EARN THEIR POWER‐UPS.
HMM.
YEAH, MAKES SENSE.
[NYAN‐TA] THAT'S A PRETTY
BRILLIANT DEDUCTION,
MISS AKATSUKI.
[NAOTSUGU]
OK, SO WHERE ARE THEY NOW?
[SHIROE] THEY'RE STILL
ON MY FRIENDS LIST.
THE SISTER IS MINORI, AND HER
YOUNGER BROTHER IS TOYA.
I SAW THEM SHORTLY AFTER
THE APOCALYPSE CAME TO PASS.
PRETTY ROUGH FOR
A COUPLE OF KIDS.
[SHIROE] BUT THEN I WOUND
UP BACK IN AKIHABARA.
EVERYTHING HAD
BECOME SUCH A MESS.
WE GOT SEPARATED
FROM EACH OTHER.
[AKATSUKI] I WAS ALSO TELEPORTED
INTO AN ABANDONED BUILDING.
(WAVES CRASHING)
[NAOTSUGU] MAYBE YOU SHOULD'VE
TRIED GETTING AHOLD OF THEM.
YOU KNOW, JUST TO MAKE
SURE THEY'RE SAFE...
[SHIROE] YEAH...
[NYAN‐TA] WELL, I'M SURE
HE HAD HIS REASONS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
[SHIROE] WE WERE GETTING
READY TO HEAD OUT HERE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAD
THE TIME TO FIND OUT.
LAST TIME I SAW THEM,
THEY LOOKED LIKE THEY
JOINED A GUILD.
[NAOTSUGU]
IS THAT RIGHT?
[SHIROE] THEY WERE
LEVEL 8 WHEN WE LEFT,
BUT THEY MIGHT ACTUALLY
BE A LITTLE HIGHER NOW.
EVERYTHING SHOULD
BE OK IF THEY HOOKED
UP WITH A GUILD.
THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE GOT TO KNOW.
[SHIROE] HMM?
[NAOTSUGU] THAT MINORI...
WAS SHE A HOTTIE?
LIKE I WOULD KNOW.
ALL I COULD SEE IN THE
GAME WAS HER AVATAR,
AND HER VOICE WASN'T
ANYTHING SPECIAL.
OH, COME ON. YOU COULD
TELL A LOT FROM A CHICK'S
VOICE IF YOU LISTEN.
[AKATSUKI]
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
[NAOTSUGU] EXCUSE ME,
I WAS TALKING TO SHIROE!
(SHIROE LAUGHS)
[AKATSUKI] SHUT UP. YOU'RE
MAKING MY TEA TASTE BAD.
[NAOTSUGU] LOOK, DUDES LIKE
CHICKS! IT'S SCIENCE!
[NAOTSUGU] HEY, SHIROE.
THE CLOUDS ARE CLOSING IN ON US.
[NYAN‐TA] I'M WITH
NAUTSUGUCCHI ON THIS ONE.
WE NEED TO GET ON THE GROUND
AND UNDER SOME SHELTER.
THIS CAT AIN'T A
FAN OF THE RAIN.
[NAOTSUGU] RIGHT.
IF I REMEMBER, THIS ZONE HAS
A VILLAGE JUST PAST THOSE WOODS.
(THUNDER)
(MOO)
[NAOTSUGU] WHERE ARE WE?
[AKATSUKI] THE SOUTH END
OF THE ARB HIGHLANDS.
(MOO)
SHIROECHI?
YES?
SO HAVE YOU BEEN
ALONE SINCE OUR
LAST EXPEDITION?
HUH?
WITHOUT JOINING
A GUILD, I MEAN.
UM, WELL, CHIEF,
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT
GUILD YOU WERE JOINING?
[SHIROE] UM, YOU KNOW,
THE CAT FOOD GUILD?
[SERARA] THE CAT FOOD
GUILD? WHAT'S THAT?
[NYAN‐TA] A PROUD ORGANIZATION
COMPRISED SOLELY OF PLAYERS
WHO PLAYED AS CAT PEOPLE.
I LOVE SITTING ON THE PORCH,
BUT THE HOUSE WAS GETTING OLD.
OR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT, YOU KNOW?
HUH?
[CAT PEOPLE] MEOW...
HOW WONDERFUL!
[NYAN‐TA] IT WAS, RIGHT UP UNTIL
THE TIME THE WEATHER GOT TO IT
AND HALF THE HOUSE COLLAPSED.
[SHIROE]
SO IT BROKE UP?
(HEAVY DOWNPOUR)
[NAOTSUGU] HELLO?
[SHIROE]
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
COULD YOU POSSIBLY
PUT US UP FOR THE NIGHT?
[MAN] OH, MY. ADVENTURERS
AT MY DOORSTEP.
NOW, THAT'S A RARE
SIGHT, INDEED.
[NAOTSUGU]
HOW'S IT GOING?
[MAN] WELCOME TO
THE VILLAGE OF ARB.
[SHIROE, THINKING]
WAIT, IS THIS GUY REALLY AN
NPC, A PERSON OF THE LAND?
MY NAME HAPPENS TO BE FEDOR,
VILLAGE OMBUDSMAN.
PLEASURE'S MINE.
AH. IT'S VERY NICE
TO MEET YOU.
THAT'S COOL. YOU GOT
A NAME AND EVERYTHING.
[SERARA] WOW!
[FEDOR] NOW, YOU KIDS GO
AHEAD AND USE THIS BARN
FOR AS LONG AS
YOU LIKE, ALL RIGHT?
[SHIROE] THANK YOU.
(NAOTSUGU GASPS)
IT'S REALLY HAY!
MOVE IT. YOU'RE
GETTING YOUR STINK ON
EVERYONE'S BEDDING.
WHATEVER!
UH, COULD I TROUBLE
YOU TO SHOW ME TO
THE HEARTH, HMM?
[FEDOR] IT'S RIGHT
OVER THERE, FELLA.
[SERARA] I'M READY
TO COOK. HOW ABOUT YOU?
[NAOTSUGU] I'M GONNA
NEED MORE THAN THAT!
[AKATSUKI] THIS IS FOR MY LORD!
[NAOTSUGU] COME ON!
[FEDOR] YOUR FRIENDS ARE
QUITE LIVELY, AREN'T THEY?
[SHIROE]
YEAH. HEH.
[FEDOR] OH. SO YOU'RE
GOING TO AKIHABARA?
[SHIROE] YES.
[FEDOR] PEOPLE OF THE LAND
LIKE US DON'T DO A WHOLE LOT
OF TRAVELING, YOU KNOW.
[NAOTSUGU] IF YOU WANT
TO HEAR A STORY OR TWO,
WE'VE GOT PLENTY.
[FEDOR] YEAH? I BET
YOU GOT TALES TALLER
THAN A GRIFFIN'S EYE.
[SHIROE] UH...
DON'T JUST STAND THERE
STARING AT OUR GUESTS.
COME ON IN.
DON'T BE AFRAID, NOW.
[KIDS] GOOD AFTERNOON!
[SHIROE] HI THERE.
[NAOTSUGU] OH, YOU
GUYS SURE ARE CUTE.
WHAT ARE YOUR NAMES?
[GIRL] MISCHA.
[BOY] IVAN.
MISCHA AND IVAN?
NICE TO MEET YOU GUYS.
[SHIROE] MM‐HMM.
(CRINGING)
[MISCHA] A NINJA?
[IVAN] A NINJA!
[MISCHA] IT'S A NINJA!
[IVAN] DO SOMETHING REALLY COOL!
DO A BACKFLIP!
KICK MY SISTER!
LOOKS LIKE THEY'VE TAKEN A
SHINE TO YOUR FRIEND THERE.
THEY'RE ALL THE
SAME SIZ‐ AH‐AH‐AH!
(MOO)
[FEDOR] THEY'RE MY
GRANDCHILDREN.
IT WAS ONE HELL OF A DAY
WHEN THEY WERE BORN.
[SHIROE]
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
10 BELOW, AND THEIR
FATHER ALREADY DECIDED
TO GO OUT IN THE
BLIZZARD TO THE MARKET.
I WAS THE ONLY MAN
HERE, SO HERE I GO
CARRYING THEIR MOTHER TO THE
DOCTOR ON THE OTHER SIDE‐
[IVAN] GRANDPA, COME HERE!
[FEDOR] WHAT IS IT?
[NAOTSUGU] THIS IS CRAZY, MAN.
EVEN THE NON‐PLAYER CHARACTERS
HAVE BACK STORIES THAT MAKE
THEM SEEM REAL, SHIROE.
(CHILDREN LAUGH)
IF I DIDN'T KNOW ANY BETTER,
I'D SWEAR I WAS TALKING
TO REAL PEOPLE.
[SHIROE] THAT'S BECAUSE YOU ARE.
[NAOTSUGU] HMM?
[SHIROE] SOFTWARE ENGINEERS
DON'T GIVE THOUSANDS
OF NPCs FAMILIES,
FEELINGS, AND MEMORIES.
WE RUN AROUND ALL OVER THE PLACE
ACTING LIKE WE'RE SUPERHEROES,
AND IN A WORLD LIKE THIS
WE CAN'T EVEN DIE NO MATTER
HOW MANY TIMES WE TRY.
SERIOUSLY.
I MEAN, DOESN'T THAT
KIND OF MAKE US
THE FREAKS AND THE
WEIRDOES IN THIS PLACE?
I GUESS SO.
[SHIROE] THEY'RE THE ONES
ACTUALLY LIVING HERE.
IT'S THEIR WORLD. THEY'RE
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
[NAOTSUGU] EVER SINCE
THIS WHOLE THING WENT DOWN,
IT SEEMS LIKE I'VE
BEEN SEEING MORE OF
THEM THAN BEFORE.
YOU THINK WE DIDN'T NOTICE
THOSE GUYS BECAUSE WE WERE
PLAYING, YOU KNOW?
[SHIROE]
AND QUESTING?
YEAH, MAYBE.
[SERARA] TA‐DA!
DINNER'S GONNA
BE AWESOME!
[NYAN‐TA]
WE TOOK THE OPPORTUNITY TO
VISIT SOME OF THE NEIGHBORS.
LUCKY FOR US, THEY WERE
NICE ENOUGH TO SELL US
SOME FOOD, NOW.
[SERARA]
ISN'T THIS GREAT?
THEY ACTUALLY SOLD US
CHEESE AND SAUSAGE!
[AKATSUKI]
SO YOU MEAN...
YOU DIDN'T USE THE
MENU TO MAKE THOSE?
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
NO, CHEESE AND SAUSAGE
ARE ACTUALLY INGREDIENTS.
AND THEY'RE REALLY TASTY
WHEN OUR CHEF COOKS 'EM.
[SERARA] WE MANAGED TO GET
BUTTER AND EGGS, TOO!
AND I ALSO GOT SALT
WHEN I WAS IN SUSUKINO.
THAT MEANS WE CAN MAKE
A BATCH OF COOKIES!
[NYAN‐TA]
MMM, RIGHT.
"COOKIES"?
WHAT ARE THOSE?
(RIBBIT)
[IVAN AND MISCHA]
OHH... MMM.
[BOTH] AH!
AH!
[IVAN] WHAT ARE THESE?
[MISCHA] SO GOOD!
[IVAN] YEAH!
(IVAN AND MISCHA GIGGLE)
[MISCHA] THESE ARE GOOD.
[SHRADER] GET MOVING!
WE NEED TO GET BACK BEFORE
THE TRIFFIDS RESPAWN.
OUR HEALER WAS SENT
TO THE CATHEDRAL.
(GROANS)
DO I LOOK LIKE I'M SOME
KIND OF DAMN BABYSITTER?
THIS IS FREAKIN' RIDICULOUS.
[ISUZU] UH!
ARE YOU OK?
SORRY, TOYA. GUESS
I JUST GOT DIZZY.
THAT GUY...
[TOYA] TWO OF US DIED TODAY
BECAUSE OF THAT JERK.
[ISUZU] YEAH, BUT
I HATE TO SAY IT,
WE'RE NOT THAT STRONG
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
[SHRADER] UNBELIEVABLE.
WELL, WE DIDN'T
HIT OUR QUOTA,
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE YOU
STUPID KIDS ARE TOO WEAK.
[TOYA] THAT'S CRAP.
IT'S BECAUSE WE'RE
LEVEL 8s AND HE'S A 28.
THAT'S WHY WE GOT
BEAT UP OUT THERE!
[ISUZU] WHAT DO
YOU MEAN, TOYA?
[TOYA] I STILL DON'T
REALLY GET IT,
BUT HE'S LIKE A MAGNET
FOR MORE POWERFUL MONSTERS.
I CAN'T PROVIDE DEFENSE
IF THEY'RE ATTACKING HIM!
[GIRL] AAH!
[TOYA] THAT'S WHY WE'RE
GETTING DESTROYED!
I GUESS THAT MAKES
SENSE. IT'S NOT FAIR.
OK. I GET IT.
THAT'S WHY SHIROE
USED THE TEACHER SYSTEM
TO LOWER HIS STATS.
[SHRADER] YOU TWO
NEED TO SHUT UP!
YOU'RE GIVING
ME A HEADACHE!
[TOYA] COME ON.
WE'RE ALMOST BACK TO
AKIHABARA. YOU CAN MAKE IT.
[ISUZU] YEAH. OK.
(THUNDER)
[MINORI] IF THEY GAVE YOU
THE RIGHT AMOUNT OF TIME,
THOSE WOUNDS WOULD
HEAL ON THEIR OWN.
THEY JUST CAN'T KEEP
RUNNING YOU OUT THERE.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR HANDS?
DO THEY HURT?
[MINORI] MY HANDS...
I JUST GOT TO GET USED
TO THE SEWING, I GUESS.
(FUMING)
MAN, WHY DID WE JOIN THIS
STINKING GUILD ANYWAY?
WE WERE STUCK.
WE WERE LOST, AND WE DIDN'T
BOTHER TO ASK ANYONE ELSE.
(CLOCK STRIKES)
[SHRADER] ALL RIGHT, YOU LITTLE
PANSIES, SHOW US YOUR HANDS.
CONSIDER YOURSELVES LUCKY.
EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE PRETTY
WORTHLESS, YOU CAN STILL
EARN 3 MEALS A DAY.
(SHRADER LAUGHS)
I WONDER WHAT... WHAT
WOULD SHIROE DO ABOUT THIS?
[TOYA] HOW WOULD HE
GET OUT OF HERE?
HUH!
BROTHER SHIROE...
[SHRADER] WELL, THAT'S
EVERYONE. LET'S GO.
AND TRY NOT TO GET
YOURSELVES KILLED TODAY.
GOT IT?
[MARIELLE]
THANKS, SHIROE!
THANK YOU!
[SHIROE] YOU DON'T NEED
TO THANK ME, MARIELLE.
[TOYA] I KNOW THAT VOICE.
IT'S GOT TO BE...
[NAOTSUGU]
LET GO OF MY NECK!
[TOYA] BROTHER SHIROE!
[SHRADER]
HEY, SHAKE A LEG, BOY.
YOU WANT TO EAT
TONIGHT, DON'T YA?
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
WE RETURNED TO AKIHABARA,
WHICH SEEMED TO BE REGAINING
A MEASURE OF PEACE.
HOWEVER, IT WAS THE KIND
OF PEACE THAT HAPPENS
WHEN THE WEAK RELINQUISH
CONTROL TO THE STRONG.
DO SOME SEE IT
AND DO NOTHING?
IS SHIROE ONE OF THEM?
WILL HE ONLY WATCH AS
THE WORLD AROUND HIM
BECOMES MORE WARPED
AND UNBALANCED?
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.