[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE CREATORS OF
"ELDER TALES" AMBITIOUSLY
MADE THE WORLD A ONE‐HALF‐SCALE
MODEL OF THE EARTH.
THE HALF GAIA PROJECT.
IN THIS WORLD, THE LAND WE
CONSIDER JAPAN IS KNOWN AS
THE CRESCENT ISLANDS OF YAMATO.
AND WE REFER TO THE FAR NORTH
AS THE EZZO EMPIRE.
[NAOTSUGU] BRIGANDIA'S THE
GUILD THAT'S BOSSING PEOPLE
AROUND IN SUSUKINO, RIGHT?
[AKATSUKI] THOSE GUYS HAD
A BAD REPUTATION BACK WHEN
THIS WAS JUST A GAME.
[NAOTSUGU] SHEESH. THEY GOT
TO BE LOVING ALL THESE
NEWBS TO PICK ON.
[SHIROE]
YES, THANK YOU.
HUH?
[SHIROE] LATER.
[NAOTSUGU]
HEY. WHAT IS IT?
[SHIROE] MARIELLE'S GONNA
DO WHAT SHE CAN TO GET
IN TOUCH WITH SERARA
AND GET BACK TO US ON IT.
WORKS FOR ME.
[AKATSUKI]
I'M CONCERNED.
IT'S GONNA BE PRETTY DANGEROUS
MEETING THEM IN THE CITY.
WE'RE BOUND TO RUN
INTO BRIGANDIA.
[SHIROE] AND IF WE'RE OUT
IN THE OPEN AND WE'RE
CLOBBERED IN A FIGHT,
WE'D REVIVE BACK IN THE
AKIHABARA CATHEDRAL.
BUT SHE WOULD REVIVE
AT THE SUSUKINO CATHEDRAL.
[AKATSUKI]
I UNDERSTAND.
[NAOTSUGU] AND THE PROBLEM
IS SHE'S ON A BRIGANDIA
GUY'S FRIEND LIST, RIGHT?
[SHIROE] YEAH.
[SHIROE] SHE'S MANAGED TO FIND
A PRIVATE ZONE TO HIDE IN
SO THEY CAN'T FIND HER,
BUT THE SECOND SHE GOES OUT,
WHOEVER THAT GUY IS CAN USE HIS
HUD TO FIND WHEREVER SHE GOES.
[NAOTSUGU] SO WHEN IT'S
TIME FOR HER, SHE HAS
TO KEEP ON RUNNING.
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI, I'D LIKE
YOU TO KEEP YOURSELF HIDDEN
WITH SNEAK AND SILENT MOVE
IF YOU WOULD, PLEASE.
[AKATUSKI] YOU DON'T
HAVE TO SAY, "PLEASE."
[SHIROE] UH.
HEH.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] SNEAK
ENABLES SELF‐CONCEALMENT,
WHILE SILENT MOVE ALLOWS
MOTION WITHOUT ANY SOUND.
THEY'RE TRACKER CLASS SKILLS.
[NAOTSUGU] ALL RIGHT!
LET'S LAY THE SMACKDOWN
ON THESE DUMMIES!
[BEEPING]
HA. WHEREVER YOU'RE HIDING,
LITTLE GIRL, I'LL FIND YOU.
[LONDARK] HOW LONG ARE
YOU GOING TO OBSESS
OVER THAT GIRL?
[DEMICAS] YOU GOT TO KEEP
A SHORT LEASH ON YOUR PETS.
AFTER ALL, YOU GOT TO LET
THEM KNOW WHO THE BOSS IS!
[RINGING]
[MAN] DEMICAS.
[DEMICAS] WHAT IS IT?
WELL, SIR, THERE ARE A COUPLE OF
STRANGERS COMING THROUGH TOWN.
[DEMICAS] STRANGERS?
[MAN] I'VE NEVER SEEN
THESE GUYS BEFORE.
[DEMICAS] HUH?
[BEEPING]
[DEMICAS] HEH HEH HEH.
[SHIROE] LOOKS LIKE
THEY JUST SAW US.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH? JUST
LOOK AT THIS PLACE.
ALL THESE BAD VIBES ARE
MESSING WITH MY MOJO.
[SHIROE]
ALL RIGHT. WE'RE HERE.
STAND WATCH, AKATSUKI.
[AKATSUKI] WILL DO.
[SHIROE]
NAOTSUGU, HANG OUT HERE.
[NAOTSUGU] ROGER.
[SERARA]
UH, HMM. HMM.
I'M SERARA OF CRESCENT
MOON ALLIANCE.
UH, I SHOULD THANK YOU
FOR COMING FOR ME.
HUH?
MEOW.
HEY. IS THAT
REALLY YOU, CHIEF?!
[NYAN‐TA] MMMYEAH.
UH!
[NYAN‐TA] WELL NOW,
IF IT ISN'T MY OLD PARTNER
IN CRIME, SHIROECHI.
THAT WOULD EXPLAIN HOW THAT
PARTY OF YOURS GOT HERE
SO QUICKLY, MMMYEAH?
UM, I, UH...
[SHIROE] YEAH, IT DOES.
I SHOULD INTRODUCE MYSELF.
I'M SHIROE. IT'S NICE
TO MEET YOU.
[NYAN‐TA] THIS ONE IS
EXTREMELY PERCEPTIVE.
IF MY BOY HERE'S LEADING
THE PARTY, THERE'S NO DOUBT
IN MY MIND IT'S GONNA WORK, AND
THAT'S A MATTER OF FACT, HMMM.
I SEE YOU'RE STILL MAKING
WITH THE CAT TALK, HUH?
STILL AT IT.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, MAN?
SHOW ME A CAT NOW WHO
DOESN'T TALK LIKE THIS,
AND I'LL SET
THEM STRAIGHT.
UH, DO THE TWO OF YOU, LIKE,
REALLY KNOW EACH OTHER?
MMM, SOMETHING LIKE
THAT, BABY. HEH HEH HEH.
SHIROECHI USED TO CHECK
ME DILIGENTLY FOR FLEAS.
[SHIROE] I MOST
CERTAINLY DID NOT!
I CAN GO BACK
TO AKIHABARA.
THAT'S GREAT, BUT
WHAT ABOUT NYAN‐TA?
[SHIROE] I'VE GOT
NAOTSUGU WITH ME.
THERE'S ALSO A GIRL
WITH US... AKATSUKI.
SHE'S A LEVEL
90 ASSASSIN.
SHE'S SCARY GOOD.
SO YOU BROUGHT
NAOTSUGUCCHI, DID YOU?
[NYAN‐TA]
AND A NEW FRIEND, TOO?
MEOW.
[SHIROE]
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED,
YOU'D PROBABLY BE BETTER
OFF COMING WITH US.
[NYAN‐TA] HEH.
WORKS FOR ME, BABY.
SUSUKINO'S A
MESS, YOU KNOW?
MAYBE IT'S A SIGN FROM
ABOVE TELLING ME TO GO
WITH YOU TO AKIHABARA.
[SERARA] HUH?
DOES THAT MEAN...?
[NYAN‐TA]
YOU KNOW IT.
THAT'S AWESOME!
[RINGING]
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI?
HMM. FROM WHERE?
[AKATSUKI] THEY'RE
COMING FROM THE NORTH.
THEY'RE SEARCHING THE TOWN
AS THEY'RE GOING THROUGH IT,
BUT THEY'RE GONNA
BE ON TOP OF YOU
IN ABOUT 5 MINUTES.
THE BOSS SEEMS TO BE A
HUGE WRESTLING FIGHTER
OF SOME KIND.
HE'S DRESSED LIKE
A MONK, BUT...
[SHIROE] HUH? A BEAR
CARVED OUT OF WOOD?
[NYAN‐TA] THAT'S
BRIGANDIA'S LEADER,
GUILD MASTER DEMICAS.
[SERARA] HUH?
(WHIMPERS)
(CHIME)
NAOTSUGU.
I'M HERE, MAN.
GOT IT. ROGER.
[SHIROE] THANKS.
LET'S GET GOING.
WE SHOULD TAKE THE
BACK WAY OUT OF HERE.
HMM?
LONDARK.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
THE OUTSIDERS REALLY
ARE HERE FOR SERARA.
[MAN] YES.
THE INTERCITY TRANSPORT
GATES STILL AREN'T WORKING,
SO THEN HOW DID
THEY GET HERE?
HUH! INTERESTING.
[LAUGHTER]
[SERARA WHIMPERING]
[SHIROE] IT'S FINE. THEY'RE
NOT GONNA TRY ANYTHING YET.
[SERARA] HUH?
[SHIROE] WE STILL CAN'T
FIND INSIDE A TOWN.
THEY'LL WAIT UNTIL WE'RE
OUTSIDE TO ATTACK,
SO WE SHOULD BE
PREPARED FOR THAT.
[SERARA] SO THEN HOW
WILL WE ESCAPE?
[SHIROE]
HMM. WE JUST LEAVE.
YOU SEE, YOUR NEW FRIENDS
FROM THE BRIGANDIA GUILD
WANT US ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE GATES.
AAH!
THAT MAKES THINGS
EASIER ACTUALLY.
YEAH, BUT...
SHIROE, UM, IF WE
GO OUT THE GATE,
THEY MIGHT
ATTACK US, RIGHT?
I WOULDN'T COUNT
ON ANYTHING LESS.
THIS IS WHAT'S
GOING ON.
THEY ARE GOING TO ATTACK US ONCE
WE'RE OUTSIDE THE CITY GATES,
AND THEY'RE GONNA
TRY AND PK US.
AND SINCE CHIEF NYAN‐TA
HELPED YOU, THEY'RE GONNA
TRY KILLING HIM FIRST.
THEY WANT HIM OUT OF THE WAY AND
YOU BACK UNDER THEIR CONTROL.
(SERARA WHIMPERS)
[SHIROE] THAT'S MUCH MORE
LIKELY THAN THEM JUST
LETTING US WALK OUT OF HERE.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
[SERARA] THERE'S A
WHOLE BUNCH OF THEM
AND ONLY A COUPLE OF US.
WE'RE GONNA DIE.
WE'RE GONNA DIE!
TAKE IT EASY,
HONEY PIE.
JUST LET SHIROECHI
HANDLE THIS, AND YOU'RE
GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
[SERARA]
YEAH, BUT, NYAN‐TA...
[BRIGANIAN 1] WE'VE LOOKING
FOR YOU, LITTLE SERARA.
HA HA HA!
(WHIMPERING)
HEH.
[SHIROE]
CHIEF NYAN‐TA.
[NYAN‐TA]
TALK TO ME.
THIS DEMICAS FELLA, YOU
THINK YOU CAN TAKE HIM OUT?
[NYAN‐TA] IS THAT EVEN
A SERIOUS QUESTION?
HMM.
[NYAN‐TA]
DON'T WORRY.
NONE OF THESE
KNUCKLEHEAD FOOLS
IS GONNA LAY A HAND
ON YOU, LITTLE LADY.
OK. SO WHICH ONE OF
YOU FUTURE DEAD GUYS IS
DEMIDOOFUS OR WHATEVER?
[SERARA] HUH? AAH!
[NYAN‐TA] SIMMER DOWN.
THAT'S KIND OF
STRONG, MY MAN.
THERE'S NO NEED TO BE SO
LOUD AND RUDE WHEN HE'S
SITTING RIGHT HERE.
WE CAN BE CIVIL
ABOUT THIS.
I BET IT'S THE
SWOLL‐UP DUDE CHILLING
RIGHT OVER THERE.
AIN'T THAT RIGHT, DEMICAS?
(WOMEN GASP)
[DEMICAS] HA! LONG TIME,
NO SEE, LITTLE LADY.
(WHIMPERING)
[DEMICAS] YOU DIDN'T
REALLY THINK I
WAS JUST GONNA
LET YOU RUN AWAY,
DID YOU?
YOU'RE MINE!
IF YOU DO THE RIGHT
THING AND COME BACK NOW,
I'LL FORGIVE YOU
AFTER A FEW VISITS
TO THE CATHEDRAL!
(WHIMPERING)
HMM. HOW COMPLETELY
ILL‐MANNERED AND
IMMATURE OF YOU.
NOW MY INNER ADULT IS
TELLING ME TO BE TOLERANT.
HOWEVER, YOU HAVE STROKED
THIS CAT THE WRONG WAY.
REAL CUTE.
[NYAN‐TA] I SAID YOU'VE GONE
TOO FAR, AND IT IS MY DUTY
TO REIN IN THE BEHAVIOR OF
CHILDREN SUCH AS YOURSELF.
IT'S TIME YOU LEARNED
TO RESPECT YOUR ELDERS.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
WHAT?! ARE YOU
KIDDING ME?
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
I'M GONNA FIGHT YOU?
[NYAN‐TA] ARE YOU
REALLY THAT AFRAID
OF FIGHTING ME ALONE?
[DEMICAS] WHAT?
[SHIROE] SORRY TO INTERRUPT
YOUR LITTLE CHIT‐CHAT.
PARDON ME, YOUR DOOFUSNESS.
[SERARA] AAH!
WE COULD GO AND FIGHT WITH
SOMEONE ELSE IF YOU'RE SCARED.
HUH?! ERR.
[SHIROE] MAYBE YOUR FRIEND
IN THE GRAY ROBE WANTS TO
STAND IN FOR YOU.
I MEAN, HE'S THE ONE
WEARING THE FANCY,
LITTLE BATHROBE
AND EVERYTHING.
YOU LOOK MORE SERIOUS
THAN YOUR BOSS DOES.
IN CASE YOU
HAVEN'T HEARD OF ME,
I AM CALLED LONDARK
OF THE GRAY STEEL.
[SHIROE] OH. THAT'S QUITE
THE FANCY NICKNAME.
NOT TOO BAD, I SUPPOSE.
I THINK IT WOULD PROPERLY
SETTLE THE SCORE HERE IF
ONLY OUR STRONGEST
FIGHTERS DID BATTLE.
CHIEF NYAN‐TA WILL
FIGHT YOU, GRAY STEEL.
MYSELF AND THE ELF
CAN FINISH THIS.
SINCE THE MEATHEAD HERE
IS TOO AFRAID TO FIGHT
ALL ALONE, THAT'LL WORK.
OK. FINE.
YOU WANT TO GET
CRUSHED, DON'T YOU?
DON'T YOU?!
HUH! AAH!
AAH!
HEH.
VERY GOOD.
YOU READY TO GET
ALL SCRATCHED UP?
MR. CAT!
[NYAN‐TA]
IF IT'S ALL THE
SAME TO YOU,
I'D RATHER NOT HAVE THE LADY
WITNESS TOO MUCH BLOOD.
JUST LET ME KNOW IF
YOU WANT ME TO TAKE IT
EASY ON YOU.
YEAH. KEEP TALKING, CAT.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
DEMICAS IS IN THE MONK CLASS,
1 OF THE 3 WARRIOR CLASSES,
SIMILAR TO GUARDIAN AND SAMURAI.
YAAH!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IN THE WORLD OF "ELDER TALES,"
VARIOUS SKILLS AND
ATTACKS HAVE ACTIVATION
PERIODS CALLED CAST TIMES.
THEY ALSO HAVE COOLDOWN
TIMES CALLED RECAST TIMES.
[DEMICAS] UGH!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
CAST TIME IS THE AMOUNT OF
TIME IT TAKES A SPELL TO
HAVE ITS FULL EFFECT
ONCE IT'S BEEN CAST.
COOLDOWN TIME IS THE
AMOUNT OF TIME IT TAKES
BEFORE YOU CAN REUSE A
SPELL AFTER IT'S BEEN CAST.
[DEMICAS] AURA SABER!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
MONKS HAVE SHORT COOLDOWNS.
THIS ALLOWS THEM TO
CREATE CHAINS OF ATTACKS,
GIVING THEIR OPPONENT
LITTLE ROOM TO RECOVER.
[DEMICAS] RAAH!
PHANTOM STEP!
HA HA!
LEAVE IT TO A CAT TO THINK
HE'S GONNA BEAT ME BY
SCRATCHING ME
WITH TOY SWORDS!
[NYAN‐TA]
CHECK YOURSELF.
A RAPIER IS A
GENTLEMAN'S WEAPON.
[SERARA] OHH! NYAN‐TA IS
RUNNING LOW ON HIT POINTS.
IT LOOKS LIKE OUR
GUILD MASTER HAS
THIS ONE SEWN UP.
UNLESS...
[DEMICAS] RAAH!
[NYAN‐TA] HA!
(DEMICAS GRUNTING)
[NYAN‐TA] HEH HEH.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER] THE PIRATE
SWORDSMAN, SWASHBUCKLER.
(DEMICAS GRUNTING)
IT'S ONE OF THE SPECIALIZED
WEAPON CLASSES AND ONE
OF THE FEW THAT
CAN DUAL WIELD.
WHAT MAKES IT TRULY UNIQUE,
THOUGH, IS THE FACT THAT IT
LOWERS THE TARGET'S
ABILITIES WITH EACH STRIKE.
LOWERED ATTACK, LOWERED DODGE,
LOWERED DEFENSE...
BIT BY BIT UNTIL AN
OPPONENT JUST CAN'T FIGHT.
[LONDARK] HE'S ABOUT
TO SUFFER A DEATH
OF A THOUSAND TINY CUTS.
WHOA! NOT GOOD!
[LONDARK, THINKING]
IT WOULD APPEAR AS
THOUGH DEMICAS IS LOSING.
[DEMICAS]
COME ON!
FIGHT LIKE A MAN!
YOU GOT TO HAVE MORE
FIGHT IN YOU THAN THAT!
[NYAN‐TA] HEH HEH.
COMING FROM YOU, THE WORDS
"FIGHT LIKE A MAN"
HAVE TO BE THE MOST
RIDICULOUS THING
I'VE EVER HEARD.
HUH?
[SHIROE] SERARA.
[SERARA] HUH?
[SHIROE]
WHEN I GIVE THE SIGNAL,
I WANT YOU TO CAST
A HEALING PULSE
ON EVERYONE.
[SERARA] HUH?
[SERARA] EVERYONE?
I'M DONE PLAYING
WITH YOU, MAN.
MAGIC USERS,
CAST HEALING ON ME!
THE REST OF YOU, JUMP THIS
CAT'S ASS AND KILL HIM NOW!
[MAN 1] AH...
[MAN 2] UH...
DO IT.
OH, RIGHT.
(SHOUTING)
ANCHOR HOWL!
(GROANING)
[DEMICAS] YOU'RE
PLAYING DIRTY, TANK BOY!
NOT BAD!
HEALER TEAMS,
HEAL DEMICAS!
[HEALERS] YEAH!
[DEMICAS] GAH! HYAH!
HEH HEH.
[LONDARK] FIGHTERS,
CONCENTRATE YOUR ATTACKS
ON THE GUARDIAN!
(FIGHTERS SHOUTING)
HE'S GONNA DIE!
[SHIROE] CAST YOUR
HEALING SPELL NOW.
HUH? RIGHT.
HEARTBEAT HEALING!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
DRUID IS ONE OF THE
HEALING CLASSES.
ONCE THEY CAST A HEALING
PULSE ON SOMEONE,
IT REMAINS IN EFFECT
FOR A SHORT TIME.
[SERARA] IT'S NOT
GOING FAST ENOUGH.
I CAN'T DO ANYMORE!
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH!
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU'S
GONNA BE FINE.
SEND THE REST OF YOUR
SPELL OVER TO NYAN‐TA.
[SERARA] OK, BUT THEY'RE
BOTH IN DANGER, AREN'T THEY?
IF YOU CAN'T HELP
THEM BOTH, THEN DON'T.
FOCUS ON WHAT YOU CAN.
IT'LL HELP.
HEAL!
[DEMICAS] HA HA HA!
WHATEVER! HYAH!
UNH!
[DEMICAS] IT MUST BE HARD
TO GET BY WITH ONE CRAPPY
HEALER, PUSSYCAT.
YOUR WHOLE TEAM OF HEALERS
CAN'T FIX YOUR HAIR.
[DEMICAS]
AW, SHUT UP!
[DEMICAS] LOOKS LIKE
YOUR WARRIOR BUDDY'S
ABOUT TO GET CREAMED.
HA HA HA!
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE!
[SERARA] HUH?
HEH.
GET READY TO CAST IT.
[SERARA] UH! RIGHT.
CASTLE OF STONE!
(FIGHTERS SHOUTING)
(FIGHTERS GROAN)
[FIGHTER] WE DIDN'T
EVEN HURT HIM!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
CASTLE OF STONE.
THIS SPELL BLOCKS ALL
DAMAGE FROM ALL OPPONENTS
FOR A 10‐SECOND
PERIOD OF TIME.
IT'S AN EMERGENCY DEFENSE THAT'S
ONLY AVAILABLE TO GUARDIANS.
HUH!
[SHIROE] OK NOW.
CAST ALL YOUR HEALING
SPELLS ON NAOTSUGU!
OK.
HEALING WIND!
[DEMICAS]
YOU BETTER STOP WASTING
OUR TIME, LITTLE GIRL!
THAT CASTLE OF STONE HAS A
10‐MINUTE COOLDOWN PERIOD.
IF HE JUST USED IT A
DEFENSIVE SKILL HE CAN'T
USE AGAIN FOR ANOTHER
10 MINUTES OR SO,
HE'S IN BAD SHAPE.
HE MUST BE STARTING TO
PANIC OR AT LEAST RUNNING
OUT OF OPTIONS IF HE
CAN'T COME UP WITH BETTER
DEFENSES THAN THAT.
[DEMICAS] WHEN THAT
SPELL RUNS OUT,
YOU'RE A DEAD MAN!
I'M GONNA ENJOY
PUNISHING YOU FOR THIS.
COUNT ON IT.
COME ON. YOU'VE GOT TO GET
HEALTHY FASTER THAN THAT!
TIGER ECHO FIST!
[SERARA]
MASTER NYAN‐TA!
[NYAN‐TA] IT'S ABOUT TIME
TO TAKE CARE OF BUSINESS.
READY, SHIROECHI?
ABSOLUTELY. READY WHEN
YOU ARE, CHIEF.
[DEMICAS] YOU FINALLY
READY TO DIE, PUNK?!
[SHIROE]
THORN BIND HOSTAGE!
(GRUNTING)
[DEMICAS]
FREAKING PLANTS!
ARE YOU KIDDING?!
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO
DO BETTER THAN THAT!
UH! HA!
COME HERE!
YAHH!
[DEMICAS] UH...
AAH!
WHA‐? IMPOSSIBLE.
OUR GUILD MASTER.
[LONDARK] THAT ATTACK TOOK
ALL OF HIS HIT POINTS.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
HEALING TEAM, RECAST NOW!
WE STILL HAVE
A CHANCE TO‐ AH!
OH, CRAP.
[COINS SCATTERING]
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
THERE IS NO SINGLE ATTACK
FROM A SWASHBUCKLER
THAT COULD EVER HOPE TO
DEFEAT A LEVEL 90 MONK.
EVEN AN ASSASSIN LIKE
MYSELF WITH THE HIGHEST
ATTACK POWER AMONG WEAPON
SPECIALIZATION CLASSES
CAN'T ACCOMPLISH THAT.
MORE THAN LIKELY,
THE SECRET LIES IN
MY LORD'S SPELL,
THORN BIND HOSTAGE.
EVERY SUCCESSFUL HIT BY
SOMEONE IN YOUR PARTY
CAUSES 1,000 HIT POINTS
DAMAGE TO THE PLAYER
BOUND BY THE SPELL.
SLASHING ALL 5 THORNS
DOES 5,000 DAMAGE.
STILL, DEMICAS HAD MORE
THAN 5,000 HIT POINTS
LEFT AND HAD HEALED
SOME PRIOR DAMAGE.
SO MY LORD KNEW THAT HE
WOULD BE ABLE TO RECAST
HIS THORN BIND HOSTAGE
WITHIN THE NEXT 15 SECONDS.
THE SWASHBUCKLER WAITED
14 SECONDS TO BEGIN
HIS ATTACK.
HE SCORED 9 HITS.
HIS FIRST 5 HITS CAME QUICKLY.
EACH SLASH WOULD
TAKE . 22 SECONDS.
AND AFTER HE SLASHED
THE FIFTH THORN,
MY LORD MUST HAVE
RECAST THE SPELL.
AND THEN HE CUT 4 MORE.
I DIDN'T SEE IT CLEARLY,
BUT IT EXPLAINS
THE 5,000 DAMAGE FOR EACH
THORN IN THE FIRST CAST,
THE ADDITIONAL 5,000
WHEN THEY WERE ALL CUT,
AND NOW 4,000 MORE PLUS
THE ONE THORN STILL ON HIS
BODY, 14,000 HIT POINTS
IN ONE ATTACK.
THAT HAD TO BE WHY NAOTSUGU
USED CASTLE OF STONE.
HE MUST HAVE KNOWN THEY
WERE GOING TO DO IT,
BUT THEY DIDN'T EVEN
COORDINATE AHEAD OF TIME.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING] INCREDIBLE.
I DON'T KNOW IF I COULD DO THAT.
[NAOTSUGU] YOU BETTER DROP
THOSE SWORDS, PUNKS!
(GROANS)
[SHIROE] WE CAME THROUGH
THE DEPTHS OF PALM
ON AN EXPEDITION TO
HELP OUR FRIENDS.
WE FIGURED OUT A
WAY TO SHORTEN TRAVEL
TIME BETWEEN CITIES,
SO YOU'RE NOT
ISOLATED ANYMORE.
AND YOU NEED TO STOP
TERRORIZING PEOPLE.
[ALL] UH...
IT'S OBVIOUS WE'VE
WON THIS FIGHT.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
WHAT'S IT GONNA BE, DEMICAS?
[DEMICAS]
UGH. YOU LITTLE PUKE.
I'M GONNA SEND ALL YOUR
SORRY ASSES THROUGH
THE CATHEDRALS ONE
TIME AFTER ANOTHER!
IT'S OVER FOR YOU!
HA!
STOP IT!
AAH!
[SERARA] HUH?
[SHIROE] SEEMS LIKE
YOU'RE THE ONE TAKING
A TRIP TO THE CATHEDRAL.
[DEMICAS] I WON'T
FORGET THIS, ENCHANTER!
I'LL BE BACK!
I'M COMING BACK FOR YOU!
HA HA HA!
[FLUTES BLOWING]
HUH?
[RUSHING AIR]
[NYAN‐TA] MY LADY,
YOUR RIDE AWAITS.
[SERARA] HUH?
[SHIROE] AKATSUKI.
HUH?
[SHIROE] LET'S MOVE OUT.
HMM.
MM‐HMM.
LET'S GO, GUYS,
BACK TO AKIHABARA!
LAST ONE THERE HAS
TO WASH MY CODPIECE!
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD,
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD!
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD...
WHAT CAN I
DO FOR YOU?
HMM.
OH, IT'S NOTHING.
RIGHT. LET'S GO
HOME TO AKIHABARA.
[AKATSUKI] YEAH.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
ON THEIR WAY BACK
TO AKIHABARA,
SHIROE AND HIS FRIENDS ENJOY
A MOMENT OF PEACE.
AND THEN NYAN‐TA
REVEALS A SHOCKING TRUTH,
A SECRET ABOUT THIS WORLD
THAT WILL CHANGE EVERYTHING
THEY THOUGHT THEY KNEW.
MEANWHILE, YOUNG CHILDREN
IN THE CITY ARE SPENDING
THEIR DAYS BEING EXPLOITED
WITH NO WAY OUT.
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.