(ROAR)
[NAOTSUGU]
DUDE! THAT'S HUGE!
[SHIROE] IT WAS ONE THING
TO VISIT THIS PLACE WHEN
ELDER TALES WAS STILL A GAME,
BUT NOW...
[AKATSUKI] YES. IT'S
DEFINITELY A LOT DIFFERENT
NOW THAT WE'RE SEEING IT
IN PERSON, MY LORD.
[SHIROE] THE DEPTHS OF PALM.
WE'VE MADE IT, GUYS.
AKATSUKI HERE.
NO ENEMIES IN SIGHT.
[NAOTSUGU]
SWEET! LET'S GO
ON AHEAD, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] MM‐HMM.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IT'S BEEN 3 DAYS SINCE
WE LEFT AKIHABARA
TO SAVE A GIRL NAMED
SERARA WHO CAN'T GET
OUT OF SUSUKINO.
GRIFFINS ARE POWERFUL
BUT HAVE LIMITS.
THEY CAN ONLY BEAR A
RIDER FOR 4 HOURS A DAY.
BE THAT AS IT MAY,
IT WOULD HAVE TAKEN
TWO WEEKS ON HORSEBACK
TO GO THE SAME DISTANCE.
WE'VE REACHED THE
TEARSTONE MOUNTAINS.
LOOK, MY LORD.
UP AHEAD.
[SHIROE]
HMM. WYVERNS.
(ROAR)
[NAOTSUGU] IT'S JUST LIKE
WE THOUGHT, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] IT'S ALMOST
A RELIEF TO KNOW
THE SPAWN POINTS FOR
MONSTERS ARE THE SAME.
LET'S TAKE
THIS UNDERGROUND.
[SHIROE] THE ONLY WAY
TO REACH EZZO,
WHERE SUSUKINO IS LOCATED,
IS TO GO OVER THESE MOUNTAINS,
THEN CROSS THE CHANNEL.
[NAOTSUGU] HIKING IS GONNA
BE DANGEROUS AND TIME‐CONSUMING.
OH!
[SHIROE]
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
UNDERGROUND.
(NAOTSUGU GROANING)
[NAOTSUGU]
THAT'S HUGE!
[SHIROE] THE DEPTHS OF PALM
IS A COMPLEX MAZE
OF ANCIENT TUNNELS
AND ABANDONED MINESHAFTS.
ONCE WE'RE THROUGH,
WE'LL BE ON THE NORTHERN
SIDE OF THE MOUNTAINS.
WHOA, MAN.
I HAD A HIGH‐DEF
VIEWER AT MY PLACE,
AND IT STILL DIDN'T
DO THIS JUSTICE.
(CRACKING)
OOH! UH!
[SHIROE] I GUESS NOT,
AND IT'S FALLING APART.
[NAOTSUGU] I DON'T REMEMBER
IT BEING A FOOTING HAZARD
IN THE GAME.
[SHIROE] HMM.
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD.
(SCREECHING)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE RAT‐LIKE PEOPLE, RAT‐MEN.
ONE OF THE MANY
TYPES OF DEMI‐HUMAN
CREATURES IN THIS WORLD.
[NAOTSUGU] LOW LEVEL,
EASY TO BEAT,
BUT JUST A NIBBLE FROM
ONE OF THESE LITTLE TURDS
WILL GIVE YOU THE PLAGUE.
[AKATSUKI]
THEY'RE NOT ATTACKING.
[SHIROE]
THEY NORMALLY WON'T ATTACK
ANYTHING THAT HAS A DISTINCT
LEVEL ADVANTAGE LIKE WE DO.
IT SHOULD BE OK,
BUT JUST REMEMBER
THAT EVEN A CORNERED
RAT WILL BITE A CAT.
THE LAST THING WE WANT TO DO
IS FACE THEM IN CONFINED SPACE.
[SHIROE AND NAOTSUGU] UH!
[AKATSUKI]
SPEAKING OF.
[SHIROE]
YEAH. LIKE THIS.
[NAOTSUGU]
HOLY CRAP. SHOULD WE,
UH, SMACK THEM AROUND?
[SHIROE] I'D LIKE
TO AVOID COMBAT,
AND FIGHTING OFF THE PLAGUE
WOULD DEFINITELY BE WORSE.
LET'S FIND
ANOTHER WAY AROUND.
AGREED.
[NAOTSUGU]
HA HA! MUCH BETTER.
[SHIROE] AH. YEAH.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, I JUST
SCOUTED THE FLOOR AHEAD.
[SHIROE] THANKS. CAN YOU
TELL ME WHAT WAS THERE,
"MISS" AKATSUKI?
[AKATSUKI] MMM...
"AKATSUKI."
[SHIROE]
UH, SORRY.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD
AND EAT, NAOTSUGU?
[NAOTSUGU] UH...
BECAUSE THE CRAPPY
FLAVOR OF NOTHINGNESS
IS DRIVING ME
FREAKING CRAZY!
IF YOU TRY TO COOK IT,
IT'S TWICE AS DISGUSTING!
(CRYING)
[SHIROE] RIGHT. NO MATTER
HOW GOOD IT LOOKS,
IT'S STILL ALL
TASTELESS HERE.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE COMMAND MENU WILL
LET YOU MAKE ANYTHING
IF YOU HAVE THE
RIGHT ITEMS.
THAT'S A CARRY‐OVER
FROM THE GAME, I GUESS.
ALL: UM.
[SHIROE] BUT THE FOOD
ALL TASTES THE SAME... AWFUL.
I'VE HEARD THAT EVEN PEOPLE
WITH THE CHEF SUBCLASS
CAN'T MAKE IT
TASTE ANY BETTER.
STRANGE THING, THOUGH... SALT,
SUGAR, FRUITS, AND VEGETABLES
ARE CONSIDERED INGREDIENTS
BY THE SYSTEM,
AND THEY ACTUALLY HAVE
THEIR ORIGINAL FLAVORS.
KNOWING THAT IS
PROGRESS, I GUESS.
[NAOTSUGU] TODAY'S
LUNCH WAS SALTY MUSH.
TODAY'S BREAKFAST
WAS SUGARY MUSH.
AND FOR DESSERT WAS MORE
MUSH WITH A SIDE OF MUSH.
I COULD USE A
DRIVE‐THROUGH OR A
VENDING MACHINE RIGHT NOW.
(RINGING)
UH?
[AKATSUKI]
WHO'S CALLING NOW,
MY LORD?
[SHIROE]
HMM. IT'S MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE] HI, SHIROE.
WHERE ARE YOU?
WAIT. WHAT?
YOU'VE MADE IT TO
DEPTHS OF PALM?
YOU'VE REALLY GONE ALL
THAT WAY IN ONLY 3 DAYS?!
[HENRIETTA]
WHAT'S THAT?!
AND IS MY PRECIOUS AKATSUKI
SAFE THERE WITH YOU, SHIROE?
(AKATSUKI GASPS)
[MARIELLE] I KNOW
YOU TOLD ME YOUR PLAN,
BUT WE'RE STILL, LIKE,
CRAZY WORRIED OVER HERE.
OK. ANY UPDATES?
HOW'S SERARA?
[MARIELLE] OH, RIGHT.
SHE CAN STILL GET
IN TOUCH WITH ME
VIA THE TELEPATHIC
LINK OR WHATEVER.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
TELEPATHIC LINKS
CAN ONLY BE USED
WITH PEOPLE ON
YOUR FRIEND LIST,
AND YOU HAVE TO BE ABLE
TO SEE THEM RIGHT IN
FRONT OF YOU TO ADD THEM.
LONG‐DISTANCE ADDS
AREN'T POSSIBLE.
[MARIELLE]
SHE SAID SHE'S HIDING WITH
THAT NICE GUY I MENTIONED
AND THAT SHE'S OK FOR NOW.
[SHIROE] HUH. THAT'S GOOD.
I'M GLAD TO HEAR IT.
[SHIROE] I GUESS THE
SITUATION IN SUSUKINO
ISN'T ALL BAD AFTER ALL.
I GUESS SO.
[SHIROE] SO SOMEONE'S
GIVING HER A HAND.
I WONDER WHO IT COULD BE.
(GASP)
[SERARA] MY MAID LEVEL IS 44.
IT WAS AT LEVEL 42 YESTERDAY.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
I JUST HAD TO GO AND PICK
THE MOST USELESS SUB‐CLASS
INSTEAD OF SKILLS
I COULD THINK OF.
I REALLY SHOULD HAVE
THOUGHT OF SOMETHING
A LITTLE MORE HANDS‐ON,
THAT MAKES THINGS OR
CREATES THINGS, YOU KNOW.
MAYBE A WEAVER OR AN ARTISAN
OR SOMETHING, BUT NO.
I KEEP LEVELING UP AS A
MAID BECAUSE I'M SO BORED.
OH, GOD, WAIT A SECOND.
THIS ISN'T REALLY SO
MUCH LIKE A MAID.
THIS IS MORE LIKE...
BEING A HOUSEWIFE!
(SCREAMS)
UH‐UH. THERE'S NO
WAY THAT'S TRUE!
MAYBE I'M A MAID WAITING
FOR MY KITTY‐CAT HUSBAND
TO COME BACK TO ME!
[MAN] HMM, SERARA.
[SERARA] AAH!
[MAN]
I'M BACK HOME, MEOW.
[SERARA] WELCOME HOME,
MASTER NYAN‐TA.
HMM. THANK YOU, BABY.
HOW WAS TOWN?
[SERARA] THE SAME.
I WAS CAREFUL.
[NYAN‐TA] IT'S GOOD TO HEAR
YOU MADE IT BACK SAFE,
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M SAYING?
I MEAN, THAT'S
WHAT MATTERS.
(THUD)
[MAN 1] WHO DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE KIDDING
WITH ALL THAT CHEERFUL
MERCHANT CRAP?
[MAN 2] YOU THINK ALL
OF YOU NON‐PLAYER CHARACTERS
CAN JUST RIP US OFF?
AND THERE'S MORE WHERE
THIS CAME FROM IF YOU TRY
STANDING UP TO BRIGANDIA.
[MAN 1] YEAH.
YOU KNOW THAT'S RIGHT.
[MAN 3] YEAH. WE OUGHT
TO MAKE THAT OUR MOTTO.
(CRASH)
[BULLY 1] HEY, LOOK AT THIS!
[MEN] HUH?
[BULLY 2] AH, YEAH. THAT'S
A SPECIAL FROM LAST YEAR...
[BULLY 3] FINDERS KEEPERS.
[BULLY 4] ARE THESE REALLY
ALL YOUR INGREDIENTS?
THIS PLACE SUCKS!
NOW, NOW. DON'T LET
IT GET TO YOU, GIRL.
THERE'S ONLY SO
MUCH YOU CAN DO.
IF YOU LET IT BOTHER YOU,
YOU'LL DRIVE YOURSELF CRAZY.
[SERARA]
UH, RIGHT.
[NYAN‐TA]
AND ONCE AGAIN, I'VE COME
HOME TO A SPARKLING HOUSE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE A
GREAT WIFE ONE DAY.
[SERARA]
WHAT? I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THAT, REALLY.
[NYAN‐TA]
HOW ARE THOSE PEOPLE
YOUR FRIENDS SENT? MEOW.
UH, RIGHT. MARIELLE
GAVE ME AN UPDATE.
THEY'RE MOVING
REAL FAST.
SHE SAID THAT
THEY'RE ALREADY PAST
THE DEPTHS OF PALM.
[SERARA] SHE SAID THEY'LL
PROBABLY ARRIVE SOMETIME
BEFORE NOON TOMORROW.
[NYAN‐TA]
THAT SOON? HMM.
RATHER IMPRESSIVE.
IN FACT, IT'S SO IMPRESSIVE
IT MAKES ME WONDER
WHAT KIND OF PEOPLE
SHE SENT OUR WAY.
(WATER RUSHING)
[MARIELLE] THANKS, AGAIN,
SHIROE. LIKE, REALLY.
JUST BE CAREFUL OUT THERE.
[SHIROE] I WILL.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
[NAOTSUGU] I SEE
YOU DIDN'T TELL HER
WE USED GRIFFINS TO
GET AHEAD ON THIS.
[SHIROE]
NO, I DIDN'T.
[NAOTSUGU]
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
[HENRIETTA] SO TELL ME, HOW DO
YOU SUPPOSE SHIROE AND HIS PARTY
ARE GOING TO CROSS THE CHANNEL?
[MARIELLE]
DON'T KNOW.
HE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT FIGURING
IT OUT ONCE THEY GOT THERE.
HE PROBABLY HAS SOME
SECRET SPECIAL PLAN.
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE ISN'T
A SITUATION HE CAN'T FIGURE OUT
IF YOU GIVE HIM
THE TIME TO DO IT.
[HENRIETTA] BUT WHY WOULD
SOMEONE WITH HIS TALENTS,
I MEAN, WHY WOULD HE
REFUSE TO JOIN A GUILD?
[MARIELLE] WELL, I'M SURE
HE HAS A GOOD REASON.
[GIRL] UM, EXCUSE ME.
[MARIELLE] HUH?
WHAT IS IT, LILIANA?
MARIELLE, THE REST OF
OUR MEMBERS ARE HERE.
[MARIELLE]
OK. DID EVERYONE COME?
[EISEL] ABOUT 60% OR SO.
NO REPLY FROM 10%.
30% REFUSED.
UH, WELL, YEAH.
OUR GUILD MASTER IS
COMING PRETTY SOON.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
JUST HANG ON A
LITTLE LONGER.
[GROUP] UH!
[MISA] WOODSTOCK W
FROM GLENDALE IS THERE,
ALONG WITH ICHIMONJINOSUKE
AKANEYA FROM RADIO MARKET.
AND THEY'RE NOT THE ONLY ONES.
ALONG WITH THEM,
SEVERAL GUILD MASTERS
OF THE SMALLER GUILDS
HAVE GOTTEN TOGETHER
IN THE CRESCENT MOON
ALLIANCE'S HALL.
[KRUSTY] IS THAT RIGHT?
[TAKAYAMA] YES.
AND ALSO, SHIROE
FROM THE DEBAUCHERY TEA
PARTY IS ON THE MOVE.
HE'S CURRENTLY
LEADING A SMALL
GROUP TO SUSUKINO.
SUSUKINO?
AH.
(SHIMMER)
[TAKAYAMA]
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
[KRUSTY] NO. DON'T
WORRY ABOUT IT.
(STONES CRUMBLING)
[NAOTSUGU]
WHOA! GOOD GRIEF!
HEY, WASN'T THIS
BRIDGE IN THE GAME?
[SHIROE] YEAH.
[NAOTSUGU] WAS IT
ALWAYS FALLING APART?
(CRACK)
OH!
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU!
AKATSUKI! STOP!
(CRACKING)
[NAOTSUGU]
GIVE ME A BREAK!
[SHIROE]
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
FIND ANOTHER WAY.
LET'S BACKTRACK ONE AT
A TIME. THAT SHOULD GET‐
UH! AKATSUKI!
(AKATSUKI GASPS)
[SHIROE] AAH!
MY LORD!
[AKATSUKI]
UH! UH!
MY LORD! MY LORD!
[SHIROE]
NOT LIKE THIS.
IF I DIE HERE, I'LL WIND
UP BACK IN AKIHABARA.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD?
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
I'VE NEVER BEEN WHAT
YOU'D CALL OUTGOING.
EVEN WHEN I WAS
WITH MY FRIENDS,
PART OF ME WAS
ALWAYS ALONE.
THAT'S WHEN I STARTED
GETTING INTO ELDER TALES.
AND THEN...
[TARAREBA]
OH, YOU'RE SHIROE, RIGHT?
I'VE HEARD ALL
ABOUT YOU.
THEY SAY YOU'RE, LIKE,
A TOTALLY AMAZING ENCHANTER.
IT IS AN HONOR, MAN!
(CROWD TALKING)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
AND THE NEXT THING I KNEW,
I WAS RECOGNIZED AS
AN EXPERIENCED,
KNOWLEDGEABLE
VETERAN OF THE GAME.
[MAN 1] THANKS, MAN.
I DID WHAT YOU SAID.
I GOT EXACTLY WHAT I NEEDED.
[WOMAN] I FOLLOWED THE
ROUTE YOU TOLD ME ABOUT,
AND IT TOTALLY WORKED!
[MAN 2] THANKS, SHIROE!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
[MAN 3] IS THAT YOU?
[MAN 4] YOU'RE INCREDIBLE.
[MAN 5]
THANKS FOR HELPING.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
BUT THERE'S TWO SIDES
TO EVERY COIN.
[KAIGANJIN] HEY, HOW DO WE
GET TO TITAN RINGS?
CAN YOU HELP ME OUT?
[MAN 1] I NEED HELP.
[MAN 2] WILL YOU HELP
ME WITH THAT NEW QUEST
IN MOGAMI, PLEASE?
[WOMAN]
TELL ME, SHIROE!
[MAN 3]
COULD YOU TAKE ME THERE?
[MAN 4] ME, TOO.
[WOMAN] COME ON, SHIROE.
[MAN 5] WELL? TELL ME.
DON'T HOLD OUT ON ME, MAN.
[MAN 6] COME ON!
COME WITH ME.
(SHIROE SIGHS)
[SHIROE] GOOD GRIEF.
[MAN 7] SERIOUSLY...
[KANAMI] THE BEST PART
ABOUT ADVENTURES
IS ALL THE NEW EXPERIENCES.
[SHIROE] HUH? OH.
[SOJIRO] EXPERIENCES?
[KANAMI] YUP. ISN'T IT AMAZING
HOW EACH NEW EXPEDITION
JUST FILLS YOUR HEART?
[NAOTSUGU] ALMOST AS
MUCH AS HOTTIES DO.
[SOJIRO]
COME ON, NAOTSUGU...
KEEP IT CLASSY IN FRONT OF
THE LADIES, WILL YOU?
[NAOTSUGU]
WHATEVER, DUDE.
YOU'RE ALREADY A CHICK
MAGNET, SO STEP OFF!
[SOJIRO] YEAH. I CAN'T HELP
IF THEY FIND ME ADORABLE.
[NAOTSUGU] I KNOW! IT'S,
LIKE, ONE OF THE MOST
UNFAIR THINGS EVER!
IT'S NOT WORTH
CRYING OVER.
[KANAMI] HA HA! WOULD
YOU LOOK AT THE SUNSET!
THIS IS WHAT WE DO THIS FOR.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL, RIGHT, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] HUH?
[KANAMI] HEY THERE.
EARTH TO SHIROE.
ARE YOU LOST IN
THOUGHT AGAIN?
SHIROE!
[SOJIRO] SHIROE?
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT'S WRONG, SHIROE?
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD! MY LORD!
[NAOTSUGU] SHIROE!
[AKATSUKI]
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
(SHIROE STAMMERS)
[NAOTSUGU]
OH, HEY, WELCOME BACK.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT,
MY LORD?
[SHIROE]
WHAT? WHERE AM I?
[NAOTSUGU] WELL, PIPSQUEAK
HERE GOT YOU OUT OF THERE.
AFTER YOUR LITTLE SWAN DIVE,
SHE JUMPED IN AFTER YOU
AND GOT YOUR HEAD
ABOVE THE WATER.
[AKATSUKI] WELL, YEAH, BUT YOU
GOT US BACK TO DRY LAND.
AND DON'T CALL ME PIPSQUEAK!
[SHIROE] I SEE.
THANKS FOR YOUR
HELP, NAOTSUGU.
AND YOU, TOO, AKATSUKI.
(AKATSUKI GASPS)
[AKATSUKI]
ME, TOO. I MEAN...
HUH?
UH... UM, THANK YOU.
[SHIROE]
UH, FOR WHAT?
[AKATSUKI]
NO, UH, THANK YOU
TO NAOTSUGU.
[NAOTSUGU] HA HA!
LOOK, BEFORE YOU GET
ALL MUSHY, WE SHOULD
GET MOVING AGAIN.
[SHIROE] RIGHT.
THIS IS CRAZY.
THAT WAS, LIKE,
A 7‐STORY DROP.
I SHOULD BE FREEZING COLD,
AND I'M BARELY HURT AT ALL.
[NAOTSUGU]
HMM. MAYBE YOU
CAN CHALK THAT UP
TO BEING IN YOUR
LEVEL 90 GAME BODY.
HMM.
[NAOTSUGU] I MEAN,
AFTER ALL THIS WALKING,
I'M HARDLY TIRED AT ALL.
SO ARE WE EVEN CLOSE
TO GETTING OUT OF HERE?
[SHIROE] WE ENDED UP
TAKING THE LONG WAY,
BUT YEAH, WE'RE CLOSE.
[AKATSUKI] YOU REALLY ARE GOOD
AT CARTOGRAPHY, AREN'T YOU?
[SHIROE]
SCRIBE IS MY SUB‐CLASS.
ON TOP OF THAT,
BACK IN THE WORLD,
I WAS ALSO A
CAD OPERATOR.
[NAOTSUGU]
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE SURE WAS.
[AKATSUKI]
"CAD"? WHAT'S CAD?
[SHIROE]
"COMPUTER‐ASSISTED DRAFTING."
I DO IT AT MY UNIVERSITY.
I'M AN ENGINEERING STUDENT.
[AKATSUKI] SO YOU'RE
A COLLEGE STUDENT?
WELL, GRADUATE SCHOOL.
I'M ABOUT TO GET
MY MASTER'S, OR I WAS.
[AKATSUKI] OK.
SO THEN I GUESS THAT MAKES YOU
AND I ROUGHLY THE SAME AGE.
RIGHT?
[SHIROE] AHH!
[NAOTSUGU] SERIOUSLY?! HO HO!
IS IT THAT SURPRISING?
[NAOTSUGU]
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?!
I MEAN, YOU LOOK
JUST LIKE A LITTLE‐
AAH! AAH!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD...
[SHIROE] SHE'S IN COLLEGE?
[AKATSUKI] MAY I INFLICT GREAT
PAIN UPON NAOTSUGU'S FACE?
I REALLY NEED YOU
TO TELL ME BEFORE YOU
DO IT NEXT TIME, OK?!
[AKATSUKI] IT'S YOUR FAULT
FOR BEING A DISGUSTING PIG!
"DISGUSTING"?
OH. I'LL SHOW‐ AAH! OH!
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, I THINK
HIS FACE MIGHT NEED MORE BLOOD.
[NAOTSUGU]
EVERY SINGLE TIME...
AT LEAST LET ME
FINISH SAYING IT.
[SHIROE] YOU'RE GONNA
MAKE HIM CRY, YOU KNOW?
UH, MY LORD, DON'T TELL
ME THAT YOU WERE ALSO
THINKING I WAS JUST A
KID IN MIDDLE SCHOOL.
[SHIROE] UH, WELL, NO,
I WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR,
BUT, UM, UH...
UH...
THAT REMINDS ME...
[SHIROE, THINKING]
IT LOOKED LIKE THEY
HAD JOINED SOME GUILD.
I WONDER IF THEY'RE OK.
I DEFINITELY NEED TO
LOOK THEM UP WHEN I
GET BACK TO AKIHABARA.
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, ARE YOU
WORRIED ABOUT SOMETHING?
[SHIROE] UH... UH,
NOTHING. SORRY.
[AKATSUKI]
THAT ISN'T TRUE.
WHENEVER YOU'RE THINKING,
YOUR FOREHEAD GETS CRINKLY.
[SHIROE] HUH?
[AKATSUKI] RIGHT UP HERE.
YOU'RE STARTING TO LOOK
LIKE AN OLD MAN.
[NAOTSUGU]
OH, BURN! HA HA HA!
[SHIROE]
WHAT ARE YOU
LAUGHING AT?!
[NAOTSUGU] HOW COULD YOU HEAR ME
WITHOUT YOUR HEARING AID?
HA HA HA!
[SHIROE] NAOTSUGU!
[NAOTSUGU] HA HA HA!
(SAND AND ROCKS GRATING)
[ALL] OH!
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S THIS?
SERVER LAG?
[SHIROE]
NO. THAT ISN'T IT.
WE SWITCHED ZONES.
[AKATSUKI]
MY LORD, WATCH OUT.
[SHIROE] UH!
[NAOTSUGU]
WHAT IS THAT THING?
IT'S TOTALLY
BLOCKING THE STAIRS.
IS THAT IN THE GAME?
[SHIROE]
A SUBSPECIES OF RAT‐MAN?
THE HUD DOESN'T HAVE
ANYTHING ON IT.
[AKATSUKI]
WHICH MEANS...
[NAOTSUGU] IT MUST BE ONE OF
THE NEW NOVASPHERE MONSTERS.
[SHIROE] IT'S HUGE,
BUT IT'S LEVEL 68.
IT LOOKS LIKE A GIANT
MASS OF DEBUFFS.
[AKATSUKI] IS IT THE REASON
THE DUNGEON'S FALLING APART?
[SHIROE] PROBABLY.
IT'S A LITTLE RISKY,
BUT WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
TAKE IT OUT.
[NAOTSUGU]
ALL RIGHT!
LET'S MAKE THIS QUICK,
STRATEGY MAN!
[AKATSUKI] HUH!
[SHIROE] UH!
[NAOTSUGU] I GOT SOMETHING
FOR YOU, RAT FACE!
(SHIMMER)
UH! UH!
[AKATSUKI]
STEALTH BLADE!
[NAOTSUGU]
CROSS SLASH!
[SHIROE] NO MATTER
HOW GOOD YOU ARE,
FIGHTING LIKE THIS
IS TOTALLY DIFFERENT!
[NAOTSUGU] NO KIDDING! YOU CAN'T
REPRODUCE THE SIZE OF THIS THING
OR ITS BAD BREATH WITH A
MONITOR AND A SET OF SPEAKERS!
COME ON!
[SHIROE]
THORN BIND HOSTAGE!
[NAOTSUGU] NICE!
[AKATSUKI] UH!
[NAOTSUGU] LOOKS LIKE IT HAS
A HIGH SHIELD RATING.
BUT WE STILL
HAVE 3 VINES LEFT.
SIC 'EM, STUMPY!
DON'T CALL ME THAT!
[NAOTSUGU] UH!
[SHIROE] LET'S MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T MISS.
MIND SHOCK!
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
ADD A CONFUSION DEBUFF
THAT LOWERS ACCURACY
AND AGILITY.
NEXT, AMPLIFY THE ATTACK POWER
OF YOUR ALLIES' WEAPONS.
(NAOTSUGU SCREAMS)
[SHIROE] KEEN EDGE.
[AKATSUKI]
THANKS FOR THAT.
GOING IN!
ONE MORE HIT AND
WE'RE DONE WITH THIS!
ASSASSINATION!
[NAOTSUGU] HUH! HUH.
[SHIROE] AWESOME.
[AKATSUKI]
THE WIND IS COLD.
[NAOTSUGU] AH HA HA!
BUT IT FEELS GREAT.
I THINK IT'S SAFE
TO SAY THE HARD
PART'S BEHIND US.
[AKATSUKI] IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
[NAOTSUGU] IT'S AMAZING.
[KANAMI] THE BEST PART
ABOUT ADVENTURES
IS ALL THE NEW EXPERIENCES.
HMM.
[SHIROE]
EXPERIENCES, HUH?
[NAOTSUGU] HUH?
[SHIROE] WHEN THIS
WAS JUST A GAME,
A LOT OF PLAYERS CAME
TO THIS SPOT AT DAWN
AND SAW IT ON A MONITOR.
BUT NOW WE'RE THE FIRST
ONES TO MAKE IT HERE.
SERIOUSLY, WE'RE
THE FIRST ADVENTURERS
TO ACTUALLY LIVE THIS.
[NAOTSUGU] HMM.
[SHIROE] HMM.
[NAOTSUGU]
YEAH. GUESS WE ARE.
YOU KNOW, ELDER TALES
HAD GREAT ARTWORK AND ALL,
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING ELSE.
[AKATSUKI] I KNOW.
IT'S LIKE THE FIRST THING WE'VE
EARNED BY WINNING A BATTLE.
(FIRE ROARS)
(SHIVERING)
[THUG 1] DID YOU REALLY THINK
YOU WERE GETTING OUT
OF SUSUKINO THAT EASY?
[THUG 2] YOU'VE GOT TO BE
THE WORLD'S BIGGEST MORON
OR JUST INCREDIBLY STUPID.
[TRAVELLER] NO!
(SLAM)
[THUG 3] FOR A BIG WAGON,
I WAS HOPING FOR A
BETTER HAUL THAN THIS.
WHAT ARE YOU
STANDING THERE FOR?
GET BUSY, WILL YOU?
[TOMTOM] I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO THIS.
[THUG 5] FINE.
THEN YOU'RE HEADED
FOR THE CATHEDRAL.
[TOMTOM] DEMICAS?
UH!
[DEMICAS] HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU,
DO WHAT I SAY, OR
YOU GET DEALT WITH.
[LONDARK] DON'T WORRY.
YOU'LL COME BACK TO LIFE.
IF PEOPLE STILL GET
UPSET OVER PKING,
THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH THEM.
[DEMICAS] HEY, GET ALL HIS GEAR
BEFORE HE DISAPPEARS
ON US, GUYS!
[MEN] RIGHT!
(METAL RATTLING)
BETTER NOT
DROP THAT.
[THUG 1] YOU HEARD HIM, NPC.
[THUG 2] YEAH. TAKE
CARE OF OUR STUFF.
HUH?
[THUG 3] FOUND SOME MORE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND, BOSS.
(NPCS CRYING)
YOU THINK THEY MIGHT
KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE GUYS
WE'RE LOOKING FOR?
HUH. NON‐PLAYER CHARACTERS
ARE CRYING NOW.
THAT WASN'T PART OF
THE GAME BEFORE.
[LONDARK]
I COULDN'T CARE LESS.
[THUG] SHOULD WE TAKE
THEM OUT, GUILD MASTER?
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
[DEMICAS] IF YOU WANT.
I DON'T CARE IF THEY'RE
PEOPLE OF THE LAND OR NOT.
THEY DON'T INTEREST ME.
ALL RIGHT, LONDARK.
WHAT ABOUT THE CAT
AND THE HEALER GIRL?
I HAVE MEN
LOOKING FOR THEM.
NOTHING YET.
UGH...
[DEMICAS] HOW LONG ARE YOU
GONNA JACK AROUND?!
YOU NEED TO BE OUT THERE
FINDING THAT GIRL
AND THAT CAT FREAK!
[MEN] YES, SIR!
(MEN PANTING)
[DEMICAS]
THIS IS MY WORLD NOW.
AND ANYONE WHO
DEFIES ME WILL PAY.
HA HA HA!
I'M COMING TO GET YOU
AND YOUR DAMN CAT!
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
BRIGANDIA IS A GUILD THAT
RUNS SUSUKINO WITH FORCE.
ITS GUILD MASTER DEMICAS
REIGNS WITH FEAR.
SHIROE'S PARTY MEETS
WITH SERARA AND TRIES
TO ESCAPE THEM.
WHAT STRATEGY DOES
SHIROE IMPLEMENT,
AND WHAT DOES AKATSUKI
SEE DURING THE BATTLE?
[SHIROE]
THIS IS OUR REALITY.