[SHIROE] I'VE COME TO GET YOU,
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA.
WHO ARE YOU
SUPPOSED TO BE?
[SHIROE] OH, YES.
MY APOLOGIES.
I'M THE LEADER OF ONE OF
THE ROUND TABLE'S 11 GUILDS.
I AM SHIROE OF LOG HORIZON.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
[MICHITAKA] HELLO THERE.
I'M MICHITAKA OF
THE MARINE AGENCY.
[KRUSTY] I'M KRUSTY...
OF D. D. D.
WHAT'S KRUSTY
DOING HERE?
[MARVESS] WHAT DO
YOU WANT, YOUNG MAN?
I'M HAVING AN IMPORTANT
GROWNUP DISCUSSION
WITH THE PRINCESS HERE,
AND I DON'T NEED‐
[SHIROE] THAT'S WHY
WE'RE ALL HERE, AS WELL.
I'VE BEEN TOLD THAT THE
PRINCESS HAS MADE A MISTAKE.
[RAYNESHIA] UH.
[MARVESS] OHH?
[SHIROE] SHE WAS ASKED TO
PREPARE SOME WAREHOUSES FOR YOU,
BUT HAS LOST YOUR LETTER
OR FORGOT IT OR SOMETHING.
NEVERTHELESS, DUE TO
THIS OVERSIGHT,
IT APPEARS WE
HAVE SOME TROUBLE.
WE HAVE QUITE A PROBLEM
ON OUR HANDS, NOW, DON'T WE?
U‐UH...
[SHIROE] I'M TOLD THAT THE
CARGO CONSISTS PRIMARILY
OF FOOD AND SPICES?
AND THAT, IF LEFT OUTSIDE, THAT
THEY'LL SPOIL RATHER QUICKLY.
THIS IS QUITE AN ORDEAL
YOU'VE CREATED, PRINCESS.
(RAYNESHIA SIGHS)
[ELISSA] SHIROE, YOU DON'T
NEED TO PUT IT ALL ON HER.
[MARVESS] HO HO!
SO AM I TO UNDERSTAND THAT
THIS ROUND TABLE OF
YOURS REPRESENTS AKIHABARA?
WELL, LET ME GET
THIS STRAIGHT, THEN.
A MISTAKE MADE BY
THE GRANDDAUGHTER
OF EASTAL'S LEADER,
WHO IS THEIR
ALLY OF COURSE,
IS SOMETHING THAT YOU WILL
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR, YES?
UH... THE ROUND TABLE HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH THIS!
IT'S MY RESPONSIBILITY
AND MINE ALONE!
(CHUCKLE)
[KRUSTY] ACTUALLY, LORD MARVESS,
YOUR LETTER WAS RECEIVED
BY THE ROUND TABLE
SOME TIME AGO.
[MARVESS AND RAYNESHIA] UH!
LET ME SEE THAT!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
(MARVESS STAMMERS)
WHAT THE‐?
THIS IS MY SIGNATURE!
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU SEEM SURPRISED,
ALMOST AS THOUGH
YOU NEVER EVEN SENT A
LETTER IN THE FIRST PLACE.
(MARVESS CRINGES)
[RAYNESHIA] THEN THAT LETTER...
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
[ELISSA] PERHAPS
SHIROE, MILADY.
OH, PISH POSH!
NEVER MIND THE LETTER.
IT'S NOT THE POINT HERE.
WHAT OF THE WAREHOUSES?
ARE THEY READY OR NOT?
[ELISSA] OH, NO.
FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND, THE
ROUND TABLE'S TRADE WAREHOUSES
ARE ALREADY FULL,
AND HAVE BEEN FOR DAYS.
[MARVESS] MY SHIP HAS 500
TONS OF PERISHABLE CARGO!
DO YOU HAVE ANY
WAY FOR ARRANGING A
TEMPERATURE‐CONTROLLED FACILITY
WITH THAT KIND OF
CAPACITY RIGHT NOW?!
UH‐OH. MICHITAKA?
IT IS TRUE THAT THE
WAREHOUSES ARE AT CAPACITY...
UH‐HUH.
[MICHITAKA] WELL,
THE ROUND TABLE'S
WAREHOUSES ANYWAY.
HOWEVER...
[MARVESS] HMM?
THE MARINE AGENCY'S WAREHOUSES
ARE HUGE AND CAN HOLD 5,000 TONS
JUST AS EASILY AS
IT CAN HOLD 500.
IF YOU WANT, I'LL LEND
YOU SOME CARTS, TOO.
(MARVESS CRINGES)
[KRUSTY] GREAT. THEN
LET'S MOVE THAT CARGO.
(MARVESS GRUMBLES)
[KRUSTY]
WAIT, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA TELL ME
THERE ISN'T ANY CARGO,
THIS WAS ALL JUST A RUSE
MEANT TO EMBARRASS
THE PRINCESS, ARE YOU?
(MARVESS CRINGES)
[KRUSTY] SORRY.
SO PREPOSTEROUS.
A NOBLEMAN OF THE PROUD
HOLY EMPIRE WESTELANDE
WOULD NEVER DO
SOMETHING SO CHILDISH.
(MARVESS CRINGES)
(GROWLING)
(CRINGING)
[MARVESS] COME NOW!
WE'RE LEAVING!
THESE PEASANTS HAVE
MADE ME FEEL UNWELL!
(SHIROE CHUCKLES)
[RAYNESHIA] UM, KRUSTY,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
[KRUSTY] IF YOU WANT TO
THANK SOMEONE, IT'S SHIROE.
HUH?
[SHIROE] IT WAS NOTHING,
JUST A LITTLE SIDE PROJECT.
SO THEN, SHALL WE GO NOW?
UH, WAIT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
[SHIROE] I TOLD YOU, RIGHT?
THAT I'VE COME TO GET YOU.
HUH?
(ROARING)
[HENRIETTA] OK, HERE WE GO!
WE WILL NOW BEGIN THE AKIHABARA
AUTUMN COLLECTION FASHION SHOW!
(GIGGLING)
OOH!
(CHEERING)
[HENRIETTA] THIS IS WONDERFUL!
SO MUCH NICER THAN THE
STAGE INSIDE THE BUILDING.
WHAT A SPLENDID IDEA, SHIROE...
AND VERY CLEVER.
OK, NOW, COME
ON, AKATSUKI.
GET ON OUT THERE
AND SMILE.
(AKATSUKI SIGHS)
[MARIELLE]
GO, GO, GO!
MY LORD...
(LIGHT SWITCH)
[PATRONS] HUH?
[MAN 1] HEY, IS THAT
PRINCESS RAYNESHIA?
[MAN 2] IT'S THE
PRINCESS. IT'S HER!
(UNICORNS WHINNY)
[KRUSTY] THERE IS
NO NEED TO KNEEL.
TONIGHT, PRINCESS
RAYNESHIA IS HERE TO ENJOY
THE FESTIVAL WITH ALL OF YOU.
TONIGHT, SHE IS A
CITIZEN OF AKIHABARA.
BUT FOR SECURITY REASONS,
SHE MUST NOT LEAVE THE
COMFORT OF THIS COUCH.
THAT SAID, SHE'S EXCITED
TO SPEAK WITH ANYONE OUT
THERE WHO WISHES TO SAY HELLO.
IT'S A ONCE‐IN‐A‐LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY,
SO I'D ADVISE YOU
TO TAKE ADVANTAGE OF IT.
[MAN] OH, SERIOUSLY?
OH, MY GOD!
OK, THEN FINE. WE'LL BE
THE FIRST ONES UP.
(CHEERING)
[MAN 1] KRUSTY WAS SO COOL
BACK THERE. WHAT A STUNT.
[MAN 2] BUT THAT SHIROE
GUY WAS SO CREEPY...
AND HE WAS EVEN MEAN
TO THE PRINCESS.
[MAN 3] WHO DOES THAT GUY
THINK HE IS ANYWAY?
[MAN 4] I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'S EVEN DOING THIS.
LOOKS LIKE THE ENEMY'S
ATTEMPTS TO CONFUSE US
HAVE FINALLY STOPPED.
DOES THAT MEAN...
DOES THAT MEAN MARVESS
WAS THE MASTERMIND BEHIND IT?
[SHIROE] I DON'T KNOW.
JUDGING BY HIS ACTIONS,
HE DIDN'T SEEM LIKE THE
MASTERMIND TYPE, NOW, DID HE?
[MINORI] SHIROE?
[SHIROE] MINORI?
[SHIROE] YOU DID VERY
WELL TODAY. THANK YOU.
[MINORI] UH, SURE!
SO, SHIROE...
[SHIROE] HMM?
I KNOW THAT A LOT'S
BEEN GOING ON,
BUT AREN'T YOU GOING TO
SAY HELLO TO THE PRINCESS?
HUH?
[MINORI] I MEAN, ALL THE
OTHER GUILD LEADERS
FROM THE ROUND TABLE
ARE ALREADY THERE, SO...
[SHIROE] WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I JUST SAW HER, DIDN'T I?
BESIDES, I'VE ALREADY DONE MY
JOB, SO I DON'T SEE MUCH NEED.
[MINORI]
YOU DID YOUR JOB?
[KRUSTY] AH...
[MARIELLE] OH, MY GOODNESS!
YOU ARE, LIKE,
JUST WAY TOO CUTE!
OH, I JUST COULD
BARELY STAND IT!
LET ME JUST RUB‐
(RAYNESHIA LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
[SHIROE] I'M NOT SURE
WHAT'S GOING ON,
BUT I'M SURE MARIELLE HAD
SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
[MINORI] ARE YOU DOING
THIS ON PURPOSE?
[SHIROE] HUH?
[MINORI] COME ON!
DID YOU TRY TO MAKE PRINCESS
RAYNESHIA NOT LIKE YOU OR WHAT?!
UH... YEAH. MAYBE.
[MINORI] HUH?
[SHIROE] IT'S JUST A LITTLE
"GOOD COP, BAD COP."
SOMETIMES YOU NEED A SITUATION
LIKE THAT TO MAKE THINGS WORK.
IN THE PRINCESS' CASE, OF COURSE
KRUSTY IS THE GOOD COP.
[MINORI, THINKING] SO HE REALLY
IS DOING IT ALL DELIBERATELY.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
HAVE SUCH AN AGGRESSIVE
PLAN TO CARRY OUT.
IT'S FOR THE BEST.
(SHIROE CHUCKLES)
[MINORI] AND YOU'RE
OK WITH THAT?
HUH? OH, YOU'RE WORRIED
PEOPLE MIGHT NOT LIKE
ALL OF LOG HORIZON
INSTEAD OF JUST ME.
[SHIROE] I CAN TALK
TO THE CHIEF TO SEE IF‐
NO, THAT'S NOT IT!
I MEAN, DOESN'T IT HURT
TO HAVE PEOPLE HATE YOU?!
[SHIROE] HUH?
(SNIFFLING)
[SHIROE] I GUESS I'VE
NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT IT.
BUT I CAN SEE I GUESS
IT MIGHT LOOK THAT WAY.
HM.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW YOU REALLY
HELPED ME OUT THIS TIME.
[SHIROE] HONESTLY, YOU DID
MORE THAN 10 OTHER PEOPLE
COULD'VE DONE IN YOUR PLACE.
I MEAN THAT.
IT'S KIND OF THE
SAME THING.
WHEN SOMEONE NEEDS
SOMETHING DONE,
AND YOU HAVE THE
ABILITY TO DO IT,
PEOPLE NEED SOMETHING FROM YOU,
AND I THINK THAT'S A GOOD THING.
HUH?
I WAS AFRAID OF EVEN MAKING
A GUILD IN THE FIRST PLACE,
[SHIROE] BUT I REALIZED...
I REALIZED THAT BEING STRONG
ON YOUR OWN IS MEANINGLESS.
TO USE YOUR POWER,
YOU NEED OTHER PEOPLE.
AND YOU NEED A WORLD WHERE
EVERYONE AROUND YOU IS
ABLE TO BE AT THEIR BEST.
OH...
AND IF THERE'S SOMETHING I
CAN DO TO HELP THAT WORLD GROW,
I'LL WORK AT LEAST
AS HARD AS YOU.
I'LL DO ALL I CAN.
MINORI, I DON'T WANT TO
CAUSE YOU ANY PROBLEMS.
I'LL DO MY BEST
TO AVOID THEM.
UH... UM, THANK YOU.
[MINORI] COME ON! DID YOU TRY
TO MAKE PRINCESS RAYNESHIA
NOT LIKE YOU OR WHAT?!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I DIDN'T KNOW.
[MINORI] I MEAN, DOESN'T IT
HURT TO HAVE PEOPLE HATE YOU?!
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I DIDN'T REALIZE.
[SHIROE] HONESTLY, YOU DID
MORE THAN 10 OTHER PEOPLE
COULD'VE DONE IN YOUR PLACE.
I MEAN THAT.
[AKATSUKI, THINKING]
I'VE BEEN WITH HIM THE
WHOLE TIME, AND I...
(SIGHS)
(SPLASH)
[SHIROE] OSHIMA?
WHERE ARE YOU?
[WOMAN] I'M SORRY.
OSHIMA WILL NOT BE HERE TONIGHT.
[SHIROE] UH...
[WOMAN] YOU ARE SHIROE, CORRECT?
MY NAME IS DARIELLA.
I'M A TRAVELING AUTHOR AND ONE
OF THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
OSHIMA IS CURRENTLY TIED UP
WITH SOMETHING AT THE MOMENT
AND SADLY UNABLE TO ATTEND.
INSTEAD, I WILL BE HAPPY TO TELL
YOU ABOUT MINAMI IN HIS PLACE.
[SHIROE] I'VE NEVER HEARD OF
THE SPELL YOU'RE USING,
BUT IT CREATES AN
INTERESTING DISGUISE...
[SHIROE] NUREHA.
(NUREHA CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
VERY WELL DONE.
WHAT GAVE ME AWAY, SHIROE, HUH?
YOU SHOULD NOT HAVE BEEN
AWARE OF MY OVERLAY YET.
[NUREHA] IT'S A RATHER COMPLEX
INFORMATION‐CONTROL SPELL.
[SHIROE] INTUITION.
[NUREHA] OH, YEAH?
(GIGGLES)
WELL, THEN I WON'T
INQUIRE FURTHER, MY DEAR.
ALTHOUGH, I AM PLEASED THAT YOU
ARE FAMILIAR WITH WHO I AM.
[SHIROE] I KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
YOU'RE THE RULER OF THE WEST.
OH, COME, NOW.
I WOULDN'T SAY I'M A RULER.
[SHIROE] NO MATTER WHAT
YOU CALL YOURSELF,
YOU ARE THE LEADER,
EVEN IF YOU'VE LEFT THE
COMMAND OF EVERYTHING BACK HOME
IN THE HANDS OF INTICS,
MIZUHA, AND ZELDYS.
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE GUILD THAT OVERSEAS
THE WESTERN CITY OF MINAMI
IS CALLED PLANT HWYADEN.
AND ITS GUILD MASTER
WHO CONTROLS EVERYTHING
TO THE WEST IS NUREHA.
(NUREHA CHUCKLES)
[SHIROE] SOON AFTER
THE APOCALYPSE,
YOU FOUND YOUR PLACE.
YOU WON THE FAVOR OF
NOBILITY IN MINAMI,
AND YOU MADE ITS
GUARDS YOUR SERVANTS.
YOU EVEN CONTROLLED
THE NOBILITY'S WEALTH,
AND THEN YOU BOUGHT
THE CATHEDRAL...
WHERE ALL THE ADVENTURERS WHO
DIE ULTIMATELY GO TO REVIVE.
[SHIROE] YOU GAINED ENORMOUS
POLITICAL AUTHORITY
AS WELL AS INFLUENCE OVER THE
VERY LIVES OF THE ADVENTURERS.
AND THEN YOU FINALLY DECLARED
THAT EVERY ADVENTURER IN MINAMI
WOULD BE FORCED TO
JOIN PLANT HWYADEN.
I'VE BEEN TOLD THERE'S
JUST ONE GUILD IN TOWN,
SO THERE'S NO COMPETITION.
IS THAT RIGHT?
(NUREHA CHUCKLES)
[NUREHA] ISN'T IT WONDERFUL?
NUREHA, WHAT BRINGS YOU
HERE TO AKIHABARA?
[NUREHA] I HAVE COME
TO INVITE YOU TO JOIN US,
TO JOIN PLANT HWYADEN.
TO BE BY MY SIDE.
[NUREHA] TO WALK WITH ME.
AND TO PROTECT ME.
[SHIROE] WHY?
[NUREHA] OH, DON'T
PLAY THE FOOL.
YOU MUST KNOW
I WANT YOU.
I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING YOUR
MOVEMENTS AND PROGRESS FOR
A LONG, LONG TIME, SHIROE.
(SHIROE CRINGES)
[NUREHA] IT'S TRUE,
AND I KNOW EVERYTHING...
INCLUDING YOUR CREATION OF
A NEW MAGIC AT ZANTLEAF.
[SHIROE] AND I KNOW QUITE
A BIT ABOUT YOU, AS WELL.
YOU RESTARTED THE TRANSPORT
GATES BETWEEN CITIES,
EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE
STILL HIGHLY UNSTABLE.
[NUREHA] WELL, JUST BECAUSE
YOU KNOW THAT DOESN'T MEAN
YOU KNOW EVERYTHING.
WAS IT YOUR ORDER TO CUT OFF
ALL INFORMATION FROM THE WEST?
[NUREHA] THAT WAS SOMETHING
MIZUHA DECIDED TO DO.
[SHIROE] PERHAPS.
AND WHAT OF DISTURBANCES
AIMED AT THE ROUND TABLE?
ONE OF MARVESS' LITTLE IDEAS
GOT A BIT OUT OF HAND...
(CHUCKLES)
THOUGH YOU DEALT
WITH IT SPLENDIDLY.
VERY WELL DONE.
(SHIROE SNARLS)
YOU KNEW ABOUT IT,
AND YOU DID NOTHING!
OH!
[NUREHA] WHY DON'T YOU BE QUIET
AND COME WITH ME, SHIROE?
[SHIROE] UHH...
[NUREHA] OH, WHY NOT?
BECAUSE NONE OF WHAT
YOU'RE SAYING IS TRUE.
OK. IF I TELL THE TRUTH,
WILL YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND?
I CAN'T SAY THAT
UNTIL YOU TELL ME.
[NUREHA] OF COURSE, IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU REALLY WANT.
THOUGH I ASSURE YOU, THE TRUTH
IS NOTHING YOU WANT TO HEAR.
BUT THEN AGAIN, YOU ARE
A SPECIAL BREED, AREN'T YOU?
[SHIROE] HMM.
I WAS SO PLAIN...
REALLY JUST A SIMPLE WOMAN.
[SHIROE] UH...
[NUREHA] I NEVER STOOD
OUT IN THE CROWD.
IT WAS AS THOUGH I WERE
NOTHING MORE THAN THE AIR.
NO ONE KNEW ME NOR
REMEMBERED MY NAME.
NO ONE EVER EVEN NOTICED
IF I WAS THERE OR NOT.
AND THEN IT HAPPENED.
THEN I DISCOVERED
"ELDER TALES."
I THOUGHT THAT HERE
IT WOULD CHANGE.
SOMEONE MIGHT SEE ME.
IN HERE, SOMEONE
MIGHT NEED ME.
BUT NO. IT WAS NO DIFFERENT
HERE THAN IN REALITY.
NO MATTER WHERE YOU ARE, THE AIR
IS STILL NOTHING BUT AIR.
HOWEVER...
THERE WAS ONE PERSON OUT THERE
WHO SEEMED TO NOTICE ME.
HE KNEW WHO I WAS. HE TOLD
ME THINGS, LIKE THAT
I WAS TALENTED.
HE TOLD ME HE RESPECTED
WHO I WAS AND HOW I MANAGED
TO PLAY SO WELL ON MY OWN.
AND WE HAD SOMETHING IN COMMON,
HE WAS AN ENCHANTER LIKE ME.
(SHIROE GASPS)
OK. SO WHO IS THIS
ENCHANTER? TELL ME.
(NUREHA GIGGLES)
I'M SORRY. I MADE
THAT PART UP.
[SHIROE] BUT WAIT... WHY?
[NUREHA] OH, SHIROE,
IS IT NOT TRUE
THAT YOU'RE ON THE
VERGE OF FINDING IT?
FINDING FRACTION,
FINDING THE WAY HOME?
[SHIROE] UH...
(NUREHA LAUGHS)
YES, YOU REALLY ARE
A SPECIAL ONE, SHIROE!
[NUREHA] A MEANS OF GOING
BACK TO OUR OWN WORLD HAS
INDEED BEEN DISCOVERED.
I CAN'T PROVE THAT
IT'S A WAY BACK YET,
[SHIROE] ONLY THAT IT CAN
MAKE SOMEONE DISAPPEAR.
[NUREHA] DON'T YOU THINK THAT
IF YOU WORKED WITH ME,
THAT THE TWO OF US COULD
PROVE IT TOGETHER?
[SHIROE] HMM.
IF YOU CAME BACK WITH
ME TO PLANT HWYADEN,
THEN YOU WOULD HAVE ACCESS
TO FAR MORE INFORMATION THAN
YOU'D EVER FIND IN AKIHABARA.
AND YOU COULD USE ALL THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND'S MONEY AND POWER
IN ANY WAY YOU SEE FIT.
[NUREHA] I THINK IT'S THE
MOST LIKELY SCENARIO FOR
YOU TO FIND A WAY HOME,
AS WELL AS THE BEST
CHANCE FOR YOU TO HELP
ALL THE WORLD'S POOR
LOST ADVENTURERS.
(SHIROE GRIMACES)
(CHUCKLES)
BESIDES...
[NUREHA] YOU DON'T ACTUALLY HAVE
ANY REAL REASON AT ALL, DO YOU?
[SHIROE] A REASON?
[NUREHA] THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU HAVE NO REASON
TO HELP AKIHABARA,
NOR ANY REASON TO HELP
THE PEOPLE OF THE LAND.
ALL YOU HAVE IS A WHISPERING,
VAGUE SENSE OF ETHICS.
HONESTLY, IT MUST BE
PAINFUL FOR YOU.
[SHIROE] UHH...
BUT THINK ABOUT
IT, SHIROE.
WHY DON'T YOU ALLOW LITTLE
OLD ME TO BE YOUR REASON?
YOU CAN USE ME AS YOUR
EXCUSE TO DO ANYTHING
YOU WANT IN THIS WORLD...
EVERYTHING YOU WANT.
(SHIROE SIGHS)
[NUREHA] AND YOU KNOW THAT
I REALLY WILL DO ANYTHING
YOU WANT, SHIROE...
WHATEVER YOU NEED
ME TO DO FOR YOU.
AND WHATEVER YOU WANT
[NUREHA] I WILL GIVE IT
TO YOU, WHATEVER YOU WANT.
BUT WHY?
AS I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
BECAUSE I WANT YOU.
JUST MAKE ME YOUR REASON
TO ACHIEVE ALL YOUR DESIRES.
[NUREHA] MAKE ME
YOUR EXCUSE.
[SHIROE] MY REASON...
(SLAP)
[NUREHA] AH!
[NUREHA] SHIROE?
IT LOOKS LIKE MY
REASON IS VERY CLEAR,
AND I WON'T LET MYSELF
MAKE IT AN EXCUSE.
[SHIROE] IF I WERE TO
DO THAT, EVERYTHING
WILL TURN INTO A LIE...
[SHIROE] EVERYTHING THAT WE'VE
WORKED SO HARD TO BUILD.
SO I WON'T DO IT. I WILL NOT
MAKE ANYONE INTO AN EXCUSE.
[SHIROE] LOOK, I MIGHT
BELIEVE EVERY ONE OF
THE LIES YOU TELL ME...
(NUREHA WHIMPERS)
[SHIROE] BUT I'M VERY SORRY.
I HAVE NO MEMORIES
OF YOU FROM BEFORE.
[NUREHA] OH...
AND EVEN IF I TOLD YOU
THAT YOU HAD TALENT,
I CAN'T USE YOU...
AS SOME EXCUSE...
[SHIROE] AND I
CANNOT GO WITH YOU.
BUT PLEASE, SHIROE!
[SHIROE] I CAN GIVE YOU WHAT
YOU WANT MORE EFFECTIVELY AS
A FOE THAN I CAN AS A FRIEND.
SO WHENEVER YOU DECIDE
WHAT YOUR REASON IS,
I WILL BE YOUR ENEMY.
OH...
[NUREHA] NOW I THINK I MIGHT
WANT YOU EVEN MORE, DEAR SHIROE.
(ECHOES)
SOMEDAY, YOU WILL BE MINE.
[MAN] OK, THIS WAY!
PUT IT OVER HERE!
[MICHITAKA] HA HA!
WELL, AIN'T THIS A SIGHT.
AW, YEAH, IT'S TIME
FOR THE GRAND FINALE.
IT'S KIND OF SAD,
THOUGH, ISN'T IT?
(MARIELLE SIGHS)
I AM SO FREAKING TIRED,
SO DESOLATE INSIDE.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHAT THE WORD
"DESOLATE" MEANS, MARIELLE?
UH...
[SERARA] I WANT TO HAVE ANOTHER
FESTIVAL SOMEDAY, MARIELLE.
[MARIELLE]
YEAH, TOTALLY!
MAYBE WE'LL HAVE, LIKE, ONE
WHENEVER WINTER ROLLS AROUND.
HAPPY CHRISTMAS, NEW YEAR'S EVE,
AND HANUKKAH, EVERYBODY.
[MARIELLE] ALSO, SETSUBUN,
AND THE DOLL FESTIVAL!
AND BOY'S DAY,
AND CAT'S DAY, TOO.
UH, AND THE OBON DANCE, TOO!
[HENRIETTA] YOU GUYS WANT TO
HAVE FESTIVALS ALL YEAR LONG!
WELL, NOW.
THEY'RE SURE
TAKING IT EASY.
[KRUSTY] WELL, THERE'S NOTHING
WRONG WITH A FESTIVAL, IS THERE?
EVERY ONCE IN A WHILE?
[MICHITAKA] THE CITY REALLY HAS
GROWN UP, HASN'T IT, GUYS?
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE IT
ALL STARTED WITH SOMETHING
SO SIMPLE AS A TASTY BURGER.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
MMM.
WHAT'S YOUR DEALIO?
GOT A PROBLEM, PIPSQUEAK?
[AKATSUKI] NOTHING'S WRONG.
[NAOTSUGU] YEAH, RIGHT.
[NYANTA] IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU'D LIKE TO SAY TO US,
SHIROE, MY MAN?
[SHIROE] UH... HUH?
YOU DO KNOW YOU CAN GIVE US
THE ORDER ANY TIME YOU WANT TO.
"GIVE THE ORDER"?
YOU ARE THE GUILD
MASTER, AFTER ALL.
[NYANTA] ALL SAID AND DONE,
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO MADE THE
CITY INTO WHAT IT IS TODAY,
AND LOTS OF PEOPLE OUT THERE
ARE VERY AWARE OF THAT FACT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
THEY BELIEVE IN YOU, SHIROE.
[SHIROE] AH...
[NYANTA] YOU HAVE THE POWER
TO TAKE EACH AND EVERY
ONE OF THEM WITH YOU
DOWN WHATEVER PATH YOU
CHOOSE TO FOLLOW.
[SHIROE] OK, CHIEF.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOUR PLAN IS,
BUT IF IT'S A FIGHT, THEN I'M
TOTALLY YOUR DUDE, DUDE!
I SHALL ACT AS YOUR
INCREDIBLY HANDSOME AND
RESPLENDENT REAR GUARD!
EVERYONE CAN JUST RELAX
AND KNOW THAT I‐
[ISUZU] YOU GOT SOME DINNER
ON YOUR SHIRT, RUDY.
[RUDY] THAT'S A FASHION CHOICE!
[ISUZU] UH...
I DON'T CARE IF IT'S
A QUEST OR NOT,
I'M WITH YOU, SHIROE!
I'LL DO MY
BEST FOR YOU!
EVERYONE...
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD?
[SHIROE] UH...
I'LL BE WITH YOU WHEREVER
YOU GO, MY LORD.
[SHIROE] I KNOW I CAN
COUNT ON YOU, AKATSUKI.
[AKATSUKI] UH... HMM!
[NAOTSUGU] IF IT'S A QUEST,
I HOPE WE GET SOME WICKED‐COOL
ITEMS THIS TIME,
MAYBE LIKE A BIG,
GIANT TREASURE CHEST,
AND IT'S FILLED WITH
LADIES UNDERWE‐
(NAOTSUGU WAILS)
[AKATSUKI] MY LORD, MAY
I SMASH THIS DISGUSTING
PERVERT IN HIS PERVERT FACE?
YOU NEVER LET ME FINISH
BEING AWESOME EVER!
(LAUGHTER)
[TOYA] OK, SO TELL US!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA
BE DOING, SHIROE?
[MINORI] ARE WE GONNA BE
REBUILDING THE OTHER TOWNS?
[RUDY] WHY DON'T WE MAKE
THE ENTIRE YAMATO ISLAND CHAIN
RIDICULOUSLY GORGEOUS? LIKE ME!
[MINORI] WELL, NO MATTER
WHAT WE END UP DOING,
WE NEED TO START
RAISING OUR LEVELS.
(GIANT GROWLS)
[NYANTA] PERHAPS WE SHOULD
FIND A WAY TO GO BACK
TO OUR OWN WORLD.
[ALL] HUH?
[SHIROE] NO.
WE'RE DOING SOMETHING
BIGGER THAN THAT.
[NAOTSUGU] OH, YEAH?
WHAT'S BIGGER THAN THAT?
[SHIROE] EVERYONE, LISTEN TO ME.
I KNOW THE NEXT GOAL
FOR LOG HORIZON.
[AKATSUKI] LEAVE IT TO ME!
RIGHT ON!
IT'S THE END FOR YOU!
(CLANG)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
THE MMORPG "ELDER TALES"...
ONE DAY, TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF PLAYERS
SUDDENLY FOUND THEMSELVES
TRAPPED WITHIN IT,
WITHIN A WORLD THAT LOOKED
JUST LIKE THE GAME.
BUT NOW IT IS OUR WORLD.
(COINS CLINK)
IT IS OUR REALITY.
AND FROM HERE,
WE WILL CHANGE IT
HOWEVER WE WANT.
[REGAN] I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR
YOU, SHIROE. I KNEW YOU'D COME.
[SHIROE] ACTUALLY...
I HAVE DECIDED THAT
I'M LEAVING AKIHABARA.
[REGAN] OH.
HMM. WOULD IT BE TOO MUCH
TO ASK IF I JOINED YOU?