(SPELL ENERGY PULSES)
[NAOTSUGU, VOICE‐CHAT]
WE'VE ALMOST CLEARED THIS AREA.
WE MIGHT HAVE MISSED A SQUAD
OR TWO, SO KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
[MINORI] UNDERSTOOD.
THERE'S A MESSAGE FROM NAOTSUGU.
LOOKS LIKE GOBLINS MIGHT
BE HEADED THIS WAY.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW IF I SEE
ANYTHING COMING. TOYA!
[TOYA] I'LL DRAW THEM OUT
WHEN THEY GET HERE, GOT IT?
[RUDY] THAT'S CRAZY. JUST
HOW FAR CAN MISS MINORI SEE WHEN
IT'S DARK LIKE THIS ANYWAY?
[SERARA] SHE'S USING SOME
MAGIC EYE DROPS THAT
NAOTSUGU LENT HER.
SHE SHOULD BE ABLE TO SEE
LIKE A CAT FOR A FULL DAY.
[MINORI, THINKING] IT'S WORKING
JUST LIKE I PLANNED.
AND IT HAS TO WORK.
I MEAN, I PRETTY MUCH DRAGGED
EVERYBODY INTO THIS.
[MARIELLE, VOICE‐CHAT]
THEY'RE ATTACKING THEM?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, NAOTSUGU?
THEY TOLD ME THEY WERE GONNA
LEAD IN THE EVACUATION!
THOSE KIDS CAN'T
DO IT ON THEIR OWN!
RIGHT. AND THAT'S WHY THEY'RE
NOT TRYING TO HOLD THEM OFF.
THAT'S WHY THEY'RE
FIGHTING THEM INSTEAD.
[MARIELLE] WHAT?
[NAOTSUGU] LOOK...
THE GOBLINS DON'T HAVE A
PLACE TO FALL BACK TO.
AND THEY HAVE
NOTHING TO PROTECT.
SO WE NEED TO TAKE
THE FIGHT TO THEM.
DIRECTLY. THAT'S THE PLAN.
[MARIELLE]
I DON'T KNOW, NAOTSUGU.
[NAOTSUGU] THEY'LL RUN
LIKE THEY ALWAYS DO
WHEN WE START
BEATING ON THEM.
THEY'RE STUPID AND CLUMSY
AND HAVE NO TRAINING,
LIKE GOBS ALWAYS ARE.
AS LONG AS THEY'RE GONNA KEEP
ON FIGHTING LIKE GOBLINS,
OUR BEST CHANCE IS TO
HIT THEM HARD AND FAST.
REALLY... WHEN YOU THINK
ABOUT IT, IT'S ACTUALLY
A PRETTY GOOD STRATEGY.
YUP, THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
AND, BESIDES, THE KIDS HAVE US
FOR BACKUP. WE GOT THIS, RIGHT?
IT'S GONNA
BE A LONG NIGHT.
YEAH, BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE DOING THIS ALONE,
THOUGH, ARE WE?
I'VE KIND OF GOT TO ADMIT IT,
RUDY, I'M GLAD THEY'RE ALL HERE.
[SHIROE] MARIELLE TELLS
ME THEY'RE GOING TO BE
DEFENDING CHOSHI.
NAOTSUGU AND HIS GROUP ARE
PREPARING A SURPRISE ATTACK.
[MICHITAKA] WHAT? BUT WE HAVEN'T
EVEN FINISHED DISCUSSING
EVERYTHING HERE YET.
IF YOU WERE OUT THERE
SEEING IT HAPPEN,
YOU PROBABLY WOULDN'T
WORRY ABOUT WHETHER
WE WERE NEGOTIATING.
OF COURSE. BUT HE DOES HAVE
A POINT ABOUT WHAT IT MIGHT
BE PERCEIVED AS...
ADVENTURERS ACTING ON THEIR OWN.
WE HAVE TO AGREE ABOUT
THIS BEFORE THE NEXT
CONFERENCE CONVENES.
[SERJIAD] A PLOT?
YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT THE
GOBLIN ATTACK IS ACTUALLY
BEING ORCHESTRATED BY
THE ADVENTURERS?
[TAIHAKU] IF THE
ADVENTURERS HAD ACTED TO
WEAKEN THEM FROM THE START,
THIS WOULD NEVER HAVE
HAPPENED IN THE FIRST PLACE.
[KRENDITT] HONESTLY,
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
TAKING INTO ACCOUNT THE EFFECTS
OF THEIR APOCALYPSE AT ALL.
[KASHIWAZAKI]
BARON KRENDITT,
RIGHT NOW IT'S IMPORTANT THAT
NO ONE WITHHOLD THEIR THOUGHTS.
THAT DOES US ABSOLUTELY
NO GOOD WHATSOEVER.
I WOULD THINK THAT'S
WHY WE'VE HELD THIS
CONFERENCE WITHOUT THEM.
[TAIHAKU] WELL, IN ALL
LIKELIHOOD, WE'RE PROBABLY GOING
TO LOSE CHOSHI BY NIGHTFALL.
AND THEN, IF THEY CONTINUE,
LORD KILIVA'S TERRITORY
IN TSUKUBA IS NEXT.
(KILIVA GROANS)
OR PERHAPS FURTHER.
[SERJIAD] MAIHAMA ITSELF?
SO WAIT, ARE THE PEOPLE
OF THE LAND STILL HAVING
THEIR SECRET LITTLE MEETING?
PROBABLY. AND I THINK
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR A WAY
TO DO THIS WITHOUT
OUR INVOLVEMENT.
[SHIROE] THEY OBVIOUSLY
HAVEN'T DECIDED.
AND THEIR PRIDE'S
ON THE LINE HERE.
AND I THINK YOU'RE
RIGHT WHEN YOU SAY THEY
DON'T WANT TO OWE
US ANYTHING.
[KRUSTY] IF HISTORY
TELLS US ANYTHING,
THEY ALREADY HAVE
SOMEONE FOR THIS JOB.
[SHIROE] RIGHT. A GROUP
EVEN MORE POWERFUL
THAN AN EQUAL NUMBER
OF ADVENTURERS...
THE IZUMO KNIGHTS. HOWEVER...
[KRENDITT] SO IT'S
JUST AS WE FEARED.
YES. THE IZUMO KNIGHTS
DISAPPEARED.
AND NO ONE KNOWS WHY.
THEY ARE GONE.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
[TAIHAKU] WE SENT
IN A NUMBER OF TEAMS
FOR RECONNAISSANCE.
AND THEY REPORTED BACK THAT
SEVERAL OF THE FORTRESSES
THAT WERE ONCE OCCUPIED
ARE NOW EMPTY.
NO CORPSES, NO SIGNS OF COMBAT.
JUST NOTHING LEFT
ON THE PREMISES.
AS TROUBLING AS IT IS,
WE MUST COME TO TERMS WITH THE
SITUATION AND MOVE FORWARD.
[KILIVA] WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE OUR
ONLY HOPE IS FOR ALL THE LORDS
TO UNITE AND ATTACK
THE GOBLINS TOGETHER.
[NOBLEMAN WITH EPAULET]
STRATEGICALLY SPEAKING,
SURROUNDING THEM IS PROBABLY
THE MOST FEASIBLE PLAN,
FORCING THEM TO LAY SIEGE
TO A WELL‐DEFENDED CITY.
AND WHEN THEY ARE TIRED,
WE SURROUND THEM WITH A LARGE
COMBINED ARMY AND THEN ATTACK.
WELL, NOW... BASED ON
WHERE THEY WERE HEADED,
IT SOUNDS LIKE THE ONLY WAY
TO ENTRAP THEM IS TO SACRIFICE
A CITY IN THE PROCESS.
WHAT?! OH, I SEE!
I SEE WHERE THIS IS GOING!
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL THAT TSUKUBA
WILL BE THE MOST LIKELY TARGET!
YOU ALL KNOW THAT!
[BALD OFFICIAL]
UNFORTUNATE. BUT UNAVOIDABLE.
HELL, NO! I WILL NOT
LET TSUKUBA BE SACRIFICED!
YOU HEAR ME?!
[SERJIAD] CALM YOURSELF,
LORD KILIVA.
I BELIEVE A RECESS IS IN ORDER.
(LOUD CLANG)
[MINORI]
THEY'RE COMING. ABOUT TEN!
I CAN SEE 2 ASSAULT
UNITS. GET READY.
TOYA'S ABOUT TO LEAD
THEM OUT INTO THE OPEN.
[RUDY] OK.
[ISUZU] RIGHT.
[SERARA] LET'S GO AHEAD
AND START THE COUNTDOWN.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1,
ZERO.
(PANTING)
[TOYA] OK!
(GOBLINS GROWLING)
[SERARA] WILLOW SPIRITS!
I'VE ROOTED THEM!
ALL RIGHT!
OK! ICICLE BLADE!
[TOYA] THANKS, RUDY! HYAH!
[ISUZU] I'M GONNA GIVE
YOU A 30‐SECOND BOOST.
TRY TO KEEP YOUR ATTACK
SPELLS SMALL FOR NOW.
[RUDY] GOT IT.
[MINORI] ANOTHER SQUAD
AT 2 O'CLOCK!
FLAMING ARROW!
(GOBLINS SCREAM)
[ISUZU] THE MASTER'S ECHO!
ABSOLUTE PERFECTION,
MISS ISUZU.
NOT NOW! WATCH YOUR COOL
DOWN AND ATTACK AGAIN
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
[RUDY] I'VE GOT THIS.
(DISTANT EXPLOSIONS)
[SHIROE] RIGHT NOW, THEY'RE
FACING THE POSSIBILITY OF
THE KNIGHTS NOT BEING HERE.
WELL, I GUESS THAT WOULD
MAKE US THEIR ONLY OTHER
OPTION NOW, WOULDN'T IT?
[SHIROE] AS LONG AS WE'RE HERE
AND POSSESS THESE ABILITIES,
WE WON'T HAVE THE LUXURY
OF AVOIDING ANY WARS
THAT MIGHT ERUPT.
HOWEVER, NEITHER US
NOR THE NOBILITY
SHOULD CONSIDER A PLAN
THAT WOULD JUST FREELY HAND OVER
SOLDIERS TO THE
OTHER THAT EASILY.
SO WE NEED TO HAVE
A TREATY OF SOME KIND,
IF I HEARD YOU RIGHT.
YES. AND WHAT THAT MEANS IS
WE'LL NEED TO AGREE IN HERE
BEFORE WE AGREE WITH THEM.
[MICHITAKA] OH, YEAH? ANOTHER
OF YOUR SNEAKY PLANS?
I'M WITH YOU,
VILLAIN BEHIND GLASSES.
[SHIROE] THIS IDEA ISN'T
EXACTLY A MAJOR COUP.
I'M ONLY SUGGESTING THAT
WE SIT DOWN AND DECIDE
WHAT OUR ROLES
ARE AHEAD OF TIME.
ALL RIGHT. WHAT
DO WE NEED TO DO?
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
THIS THING WITH THE GOBLINS...
I'VE NEVER SEEN FATHER
LOOK SO SERIOUS BEFORE.
HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE
GOING TO GET HURT?
[NOBLEMAN WITH EPAULET]
IT WILL HAVE TO BE TSUKUBA.
IT IS A WELL‐DEFENDED CITY,
AND IT SHOULD BE ABLE TO
LAST QUITE A LONG TIME.
[KASHIWAZAKI] SO WHO'S
BREAKING THE NEWS TO KILIVA?
HE ISN'T GOING TO SIMPLY LOSE
A FEW VILLAGES AROUND TOWN.
I DON'T THINK MANY OF
HIS PEOPLE WILL SURVIVE.
WE'VE ALL BEEN
THINKING ABOUT IT,
BUT NONE OF US
HAVE SAID IT YET.
WE MUST TRULY CONSIDER BRINGING
IN THE ADVENTURERS ON THIS.
OF COURSE. I MEAN, IF THEY DIE,
THEY SIMPLY RETURN TO LIFE.
AND THE DOWNSIDE IS, WELL, WE
WOULD BE LARGELY IN THEIR DEBT.
I KNOW, WHICH IS WHY WE
CANNOT TELL THEM ANYTHING
BUT GET AS MUCH INFORMATION
FROM THEM THAT WE CAN.
AS FAR AS THE SITUATION WITH
THE KNIGHTS IS CONCERNED,
WE MUST KEEP THAT
TO OURSELVES.
[RAYNESHIA] UH!
[KASHIWAZAKI] I DON'T KNOW A
THING ABOUT THOSE ADVENTURERS.
SO IF I HAVE TO LIE TO A FEW OF
THEM TO KEEP THEIR PROTECTION,
I WILL DO SO WITHOUT HESITATION.
[MICHITAKA] SO THEY FINALLY
BROKE DOWN AND CALLED US, HUH?
[KRUSTY] LOOKS LIKE THE WEST
WIND BRIGADE MADE IT IN, TOO.
YEAH. SOUJIRO JUST LET
ME KNOW ABOUT IT.
[SOUJIRO] IT'S HUGE.
[SHIROE] THEY'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
THEY CAN'T GET IN UNTIL
THE CONFERENCE IS OVER.
[KRUSTY] WELL, HELLO, PRINCESS.
ISN'T IT PAST YOUR BEDTIME?
[RAYNESHIA]
HM. UH, LOOK, I‐
SOMETHING HAS
YOU CONCERNED.
YOU LOOKING FOR A WARM GLASS
OF MILK OR SOMETHING?
AH!
(GROANS)
[RAYNESHIA] SAY WHAT YOU
WANT ABOUT ME BEING LAZY,
EVEN A COWARD,
AND THAT I DON'T CARE ABOUT
ANYTHING EXCEPT SLEEPING...
BUT I AM ALSO A MEMBER OF
THE HIGH LORD'S FAMILY.
AND I DON'T ALWAYS SLEEP EASILY.
[KRUSTY] SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
SERIOUSLY, THEN...
WHAT'S ON YOUR MIND THAT WOULD
KEEP YOU UP SO LATE TONIGHT?
[RAYNESHIA] AH. HM.
[RAYNESHIA] I REMEMBER
YOU SAYING ONCE
THAT FREEDOM REQUIRES
A PERSON TO BE RESOLUTE.
[KRUSTY] THAT'S TRUE.
[RAYNESHIA] WELL, I HAVEN'T
FORGOTTEN WHAT YOU SAID.
I JUST THOUGHT
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
[MINORI] YES, WE'RE FINE,
REALLY.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE TOOK CARE OF
ALL THE GOBLINS AROUND HERE.
AND WE'RE GETTING A CHANCE
TO REST RIGHT NOW.
THEY'RE STILL HEADING
NORTH‐NORTHWEST, YES? RIGHT.
ABOUT 3 CLICKS.
ROGER THAT.
YOU AND NYANTA TAKE CARE OF
YOURSELVES, OK?
[RUDY] MAGE'S GAUNTLETS?
[MINORI] NYANTA IDENTIFIED THEM
AND TOLD ME WHAT THEY WERE FOR.
THEY'RE JUST THE THING
FOR PEOPLE WHO USE
OFFENSIVE MAGICAL ATTACK SPELLS.
YOU CAN USE THEM ONCE YOU'VE
GOTTEN TO LEVEL 25.
[TOYA] LEVEL 25? JEEZ. HOW GOOD
CAN SOMETHING THAT PUNY BE?
YEAH, BUT THEY'RE THE
FIRST ITEM FOR ALL OF US
TO ACQUIRE BY WORKING TOGETHER.
HM. YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT.
[ISUZU] WE SPENT ALL THAT TIME
IN THE DUNGEON TO GET THEM.
THAT MAKES THEM PRETTY
COOL IF YOU ASK ME.
I MEAN, COME ON!
[RUDY] YUP,
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
[TOYA] OK! SO WHAT
DO WE DO WITH THEM?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE CAN ALL USE
THEM AT THE SAME TIME.
[ALL] HMM.
[ISUZU] GUYS...
[GROUP] HUH?
I KNOW! WHY DON'T WE
GIVE THEM TO RUDY?
[RUDY] HUH?
[ISUZU] THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE FOR PEOPLE WHO USE
ATTACK MAGIC, RIGHT?
[MINORI] YEAH, THEY ARE.
AND SINCE WE ONLY
HAVE ONE SORCERER...
WOW! I DON'T KNOW
IF I DESERVE IT.
[TOYA] THAT ISN'T LIKE YOU,
RUDY, ALL MODEST AND STUFF.
[RUDY]
OH SHUT IT, TOYA!
ARE YOU GUYS SURE?
I WANT TO DESERVE THEM.
AH...
[ISUZU] THEY LOOK
REALLY GOOD ON YOU.
[RUDY] HUH?
(CHUCKLES)
[MINORI] IT'S TIME TO GO. WE
NEED TO MOVE DOWN TO THE RAVINE.
AND LET'S REMEMBER OUR PATROL
OVERWATCH TECHNIQUES.
[RUDY] OK, I SWEAR
BY THESE GAUNTLETS,
I'LL BEAT EVEN
MORE GOBLINS!
[ISUZU] DON'T GET
TOO EXCITED.
[RUDY] COME ON! YOU GOT
TO HAVE SOME ENTHUSIASM.
[ISUZU] HM.
[ISUZU] SURE. LET'S GET 'EM.
[KRENDITT] GENTLEMEN, THANK
YOU FOR JOINING US HERE.
THE LORDS OF EASTAL APPRECIATE
YOUR PARTICIPATION
IN THIS MEETING, OF COURSE.
BUT OUR CURRENT...
[MICHITAKA] GOOD GRIEF.
THIS ISN'T GETTING US ANYWHERE.
[SHIROE] I'M GUESSING
HE'S WAITING FOR ONE
OF US TO SPEAK UP, YES?
BOTH OF US AND THE NOBLES WANT
INFORMATION ABOUT EACH OTHER
WITHOUT SACRIFICING
OUR OWN SECRETS.
SO, OF COURSE, WE SHOULD GO
WITH THE PLAN WE DISCUSSED.
IF I OFFER TO SEND
IN OUR OWN TROOPS,
THEY'RE GONNA HAVE
TO TELL US WHAT THEIR
TACTICAL SITUATION IS.
[SHIROE, THINKING] ALL RIGHT,
GENTLEMEN, THIS GAME OF CAT
AND MOUSE IS FUN, BUT...
CAN ANYONE HERE SUMMON
THE KNIGHTS OF IZUMO?
WE NEED TO WORK WITH THEM.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL
TAKE THAT AS A "NO."
WELL, THEN IT APPEARS TO
ME AS IF THE IZUMO KNIGHTS
ARE FAILING YOU.
THEY SHOULD BE
RUSHING TO YOUR AID.
[KRENDITT] THE IZUMO KNIGHTS
WON'T SHOW UP HERE
TO SIMPLY ERADICATE A
FEW SNARLING MONSTERS!
ADVENTURERS HAVE FAR MORE
EXPERIENCE WITH GOBLINS.
AFTER ALL, IT'S NOT LIKE
YOUR PEOPLE AREN'T IN
TROUBLE, TOO, YOU KNOW.
[KRUSTY] SO YOU'RE ASKING US TO
SEND PEOPLE TO HELP YOU FIGHT.
[KRENDITT] WELL,
YOU KNOW, I...
[MICHITAKA] ALL RIGHT. LOOK,
I THOUGHT THE PURPOSE OF
THIS CONFERENCE WAS TO SHARE
THOUGHTS ON HOW TO HANDLE THIS.
BUT IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE YOU'RE
JUST INTERESTED IN GRILLING US!
[NOBLEMAN WITH EPAULET]
EXCUSE ME. THE AKIHABARA
KNIGHTS ARE SAID TO BE BRAVE
AND UNMATCHED IN COMBAT!
[SHIROE] IF BY "KNIGHTS,"
YOU ARE REFERRING TO
MILITARY OFFICERS
WHO ARE ALWAYS AT THE
READY TO FIGHT BATTLES...
THEN THERE SEEMS TO HAVE BEEN
A MISUNDERSTANDING, SIR.
AS A GROUP, WE ADVENTURERS
DO NOT HAVE AN ARMY.
THEN TELL ME, WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU ADVENTURERS GOOD FOR?
WHAT THE HELL DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT?
[KILIVA]
GIVE ME A BREAK!
YOU ADVENTURERS HAVE
BEEN BLESSED WITH
SPECIAL ABILITIES
FROM THE GODS!
YOU HAVE A DUTY
TO PROTECT THE LAND!
[MICHITAKA] OH, YEAH?
WELL, THAT'S NEWS TO ME, PAL.
THAT IS UTTER NONSENSE,
AND YOU KNOW IT!
YOU ARE INVINCIBLE!
AND DESPITE SUCH AN
INCREDIBLE GIFT,
YOU BLINDLY ABANDON
THE RESPONSIBILITIES
THAT COME WITH IT!
YOU SHOULD BE ASHAMED
OF YOURSELVES.
[MICHITAKA] SHUT YOUR MOUTH!
[KILIVA] GUH...
[MICHITAKA] FIRST OF ALL,
LAST I CHECKED,
NONE OF US ARE CITIZENS
OF THE FREEDOM CITIES!
THAT'S WHY YOU'VE NEVER BOTHERED
TO INVITE US TO ATTEND
ONE OF YOUR LITTLE
CONFERENCES HERE BEFORE!
SOUND ABOUT RIGHT?!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SORT OF PLAN
YOU GUYS HAVE UP TO THIS POINT,
BUT THE ADVENTURERS HAVE NO
OBLIGATION TO BE ANY PART OF IT!
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE
WITH THAT, BARON KRENDITT?!
[KRENDITT] MR. MICHITAKA,
THE POINT WE'RE TRYING
TO GET ACROSS...
THAT IS TO SAY...
(TAIHAKU GROWLS)
GENTLEMEN, IN SPITE OF
WHAT SOME OF US HAVE SAID,
WE ARE NOT HERE TO REQUEST OR
DEMAND FIGHTERS FROM AKIHABARA.
REALLY? YOU'RE TELLING
ME THAT WE WERE INVITED
TO THIS CONFERENCE TO LISTEN
TO LORD KILIVA'S REQUEST,
AND THE LEAGUE OF FREEDOM
CITIES DISAGREES WITH HIM?
THAT'S A BIT PRESUMPTUOUS.
WHAT? ARE YOU ACCUSING ME
OF ACTING FOR MY OWN BENEFIT?
THAT IS AN INSULT TO ME AND
EVERYONE ELSE AT THIS TABLE!
[TAIHAKU] IT IS NOT
THE WILL OF THE LEAGUE.
BUT MANY OF US DO, INDEED,
SHARE LORD KILIVA'S CONCERN
ABOUT WHAT YOUR ROLE
IN THIS MIGHT BE.
WILL THE MIGHTY AND ALL‐POWERFUL
WARRIORS OF AKIHABARA
SIT THIS ONE OUT AND STAND
IDLY BY WHILE YAMATO FACES
CERTAIN DISASTER?
WE ARE NOT YOUR
STINKING GUARD DOGS.
[MICHITAKA] "OH, YOU GUYS
HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE.
GO AND KILL THE
GOBLINS FOR US."
WHAT KIND OF CRAP IS THAT?
JUST SENDING PEOPLE OUT
TO THE BATTLEFIELD TO DO
YOUR WORK FOR YOU IS DISGUSTING.
AND IT WON'T GAIN THE TRUST
OF THE PEOPLE OF AKIHABARA!
SORRY ABOUT THE TABLE.
[SHIROE, THINKING] MICHITAKA,
ALL OF US ADVENTURERS RISK
LOSING OUR MEMORIES WHEN WE DIE.
ANYONE WOULD GET UPSET
ABOUT THAT, NOT JUST YOU.
AND WHILE WE DID WANT
YOU TO PLAY THE VOICE
AGAINST SENDING TROOPS...
YOU MIGHT HAVE GONE JUST A
BIT OVERBOARD THERE, BUDDY.
I THINK MICHITAKA MIGHT
HAVE JUST BOXED US IN.
(FOOTSTEPS)
[AKATSUKI] HUH?
[SERJIAD] HM?
[SERJIAD] RAYNESHIA...
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
OK, DEEP BREATHS HERE.
YOU ARE LOOKING
EXQUISITE, MADAM.
LIKE A FAIRY ON A LAKE
REFLECTING IN THE MOONLIGHT.
(LAUGHTER)
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING]
I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME.
I DON'T BELONG.
WHAT AM I DOING?
(EXHALES)
I JUST WANT TO GO TO BED.
I WANT TO WEAR MY PAJAMAS
AND JUST WISH THIS AWAY.
[KRUSTY] THE WARM MILK'S
IN THE KITCHEN, PRINCESS.
[RAYNESHIA, THINKING] UH! NO!
NO, GET OUT OF MY HEAD!
I DID NOT JUST HEAR THAT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I ALREADY KNOW I'D
RATHER BE ASLEEP, BUT...
[SERJIAD] RAYNESHIA...
MASTER KRUSTY.
HM? YES, YOUR MAJESTY?
[RAYNESHIA] I AM
GOING TO AKIHABARA.
AND I NEED YOU TO TAKE ME.
[KRUSTY] HUH?
[NOBLEMAN] WHAT?
THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS...
[KRENDITT] WHAT IS
THE MEANING OF THIS?
[KRUSTY] I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY AKIHABARA?
[RAYNESHIA] TO RAISE
A VOLUNTEER ARMY.
[TAIHAKU, THINKING]
RIDICULOUS.
WHAT CAN ONE GIRL DO?
[KRENDITT, THINKING] SPEAKING
TO A FOREIGN BAND OF FIGHTERS
WITHOUT AUTHORIZATION?
SHE DOESN'T HAVE
PERMISSION TO DO THAT.
[KASHIWAZAKI, THINKING]
A REPRESENTATIVE FROM
THE ROUND TABLE
WILL BE ACCOMPANYING HER...
THAT COULD CHANGE
THINGS DRASTICALLY.
ARE YOU SURE? THAT'S
GOING TO BE AN ENORMOUS
UNDERTAKING, YOU KNOW?
[RAYNESHIA] YES.
AND WHY EXACTLY ARE
YOU INTERESTED?
YOU SAID THAT
ADVENTURERS WERE FREE.
THEY ARE FREE TO DO
AS THEY WISH.
I MAY BE NOTHING BUT
A STUPID GIRL TO YOU...
WHO ISN'T SUPPOSED TO KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT POLITICS.
HOWEVER, I WAS TAUGHT FROM
A VERY YOUNG AGE THAT YOU
SHOW RESPECT WHEN YOU ASK
FOR SOMETHING YOU WANT.
AND AS A MEMBER OF THIS FAMILY,
MY FATHER AND MY GRANDFATHER
INGRAINED THIS IN ME.
THAT'S WHY.
I THINK IT'S IMPROPER THAT WE
SHOULD BE HIDING THE TRUTH.
THE FOREMOST TRUTH BEING WE
CAN'T FIND THE IZUMO KNIGHTS!
(REPRESENTATIVES
SPEAKING AT ONCE)
[TAIHAKU] TOLD THEM
OUR SECRET, OF COURSE!
YOU REALLY KNOW HOW TO
BREAK UP A PARTY, DON'T YOU?
WHEN I TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY,
I WANT YOU TO
APOLOGIZE WITH ME.
ALL RIGHT. WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU PLANNING, PRINCESS?
[RAYNESHIA] I GUESS
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS READ
MY MIND NOW, CAN YOU?
WELL, THERE IS NO PLAN.
IN FACT, I DON'T KNOW HOW
I'M GONNA PULL THIS OFF,
BUT AS A MEMBER OF
THE COWEN FAMILY,
I CERTAINLY DO NOT WISH TO
BE INSULTING TO EVERYONE.
(CLAP RESOUNDS)
(CHATTER STOPS)
[RAYNESHIA] GRANDFATHER?
[SERJIAD] YOU HAVE THE FLOOR.
[RAYNESHIA]
THE ADVENTURERS ARE FREE.
THEY HAVE MORE FREEDOM THAN ANY
OF US COULD EVER HOPE TO HAVE.
I DON'T KNOW ANYONE AMONG
US WHO IS ANYWHERE NEAR AS
STRONG AS AN ADVENTURER IS,
BUT THAT DOES NOT MEAN THAT WE
JUST GET TO TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THEM WHENEVER WE WANT.
WE DON'T HAVE THE RIGHT
TO EXPLOIT ANYONE ELSE.
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER
HOW POWERFUL THEY ARE
OR HOW WEAK WE ARE.
THE TIME TO ASK
THEM IS NOW.
BUT I NEED TO GO TO AKIHABARA
WITH AN OPEN HEART.
MASTER KRUSTY SAID THAT EVERY
SINGLE ADVENTURER HAS FREEDOM.
SO IF ANY OF THEM WOULD
AGREE FREELY TO HELP US,
THEN WHY WOULD WE NOT
ENCOURAGE THAT TO HAPPEN?
EVEN IF I JUST FIND A DOZEN,
IT HAS TO BE WORTH THE TIME
I SPEND THERE, RIGHT?
MY GRANDFATHER TAUGHT ME
THAT THE REAL ART OF SHOWING
SOMEONE RESPECT ISN'T ABOUT
FANCY OR FORCEFUL TALKING.
I WILL GO THERE.
AND I'LL TALK TO EVERY SINGLE
ONE OF THEM IF I HAVE TO.
I'LL DO WHATEVER IT TAKES.
(GASP)
[KRUSTY] PRINCESS!
[SHIROE] PRINCESS RAYNESHIA!
[KRUSTY] IT'S FINE. I THINK
SHE WAS JUST NERVOUS.
SO I GUESS I'LL JUST LEAVE
THE REST OF THIS TO YOU.
NO WAY, MAN.
SHE'S GOING WITH YOU.
I'M SURE YOU'LL
HANDLE IT.
HUH?
[SHIROE] SHE'S MADE
HER DECISION.
THE QUESTION IS, ARE YOU GOING
TO ABIDE BY IT, "MASTER" KRUSTY?
(LOUD ROAR)
[GROUP] HUH?!
(BUSHES RUSTLING)
(SERARA GASPS)
[TOYA] A BIRD?
(GIRLS CHUCKLE)
IT'S JUST A GIANT
TURKEY. NO BIGGIE.
GUESS THE NIGHTTIME'S
STILL A LITTLE SCARY, HUH?
[MINORI, THINKING]
HE'S RIGHT...
IT'S STILL DANGEROUS
OUT HERE FOR US.
WE REALLY HAVEN'T DEFEATED
VERY MANY ENEMIES.
WE NEED TO BE CAREFUL,
ALL OF US.
[TOYA] WHAT SCARES ME IS
HITTING SOFT GROUND, ROOTS,
AND ROCKS WHILE I'M
TRYING TO FIGHT.
[ISUZU] TELL ME ABOUT IT. IT'S
SO EASY TO LOSE YOUR BALANCE.
[SERARA] I'M ALWAYS ANXIOUS
BECAUSE I NEVER KNOW WHEN
THE ENEMY WILL APPEAR.
[TOYA] I THINK WE'RE ALL A BIT
MORE WEARY OF GOBLINS AT NIGHT,
BUT AT LEAST WE CAN
SMELL THEM COMING.
[RUDY] YEAH, AND
IT'S NOT A GOOD SMELL.
IT'S SUPER NASTY.
[TOYA] IT SURE IS.
BUT IN A WEIRD WAY, IT MAKES
ME WANT TO GO OUT THERE
AND FIGHT EVEN HARDER!
[ISUZU] YEAH! I CAN
GO ALONG WITH THAT.
[RUDY] THIS IS
WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT...
HELPING THOSE IN TROUBLE,
LEAVING NO MAN BEHIND.
IT'S WHAT MAKES US ADVENTURERS.
[ISUZU] MHM.
[MINORI, THINKING] YEAH.
WE REALLY DON'T NEED TO
OVERTHINK THIS ALL THAT MUCH.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO FOR NOW
IS GO OUT AND PROTECT THE
PEOPLE WE CARE FOR.
LET'S WIPE OUT THESE GOBLINS
AND BE DONE WITH IT.
AND AS A SHRINE MAIDEN,
I'LL JUST DO MY JOB.
AND THAT'S TO KEEP
EVERYBODY SAFE.
(GRIFFIN SCREECHES)
(RAYNESHIA WHIMPERING)
(SHIROE CHUCKLES)
[AKATSUKI] IS THERE
SOMETHING AMUSING, MY LORD?
[SHIROE] KRUSTY IS TOTALLY
BESIDE HIMSELF RIGHT NOW.
HE WAS COMPLETELY OVERWHELMED.
I NEVER EXPECTED THE
PRINCESS TO STAND UP TO
THOSE NOBLES LIKE THAT.
I'M IMPRESSED.
IT'S ABOUT RESPECT.
[AKATSUKI] RESPECT?
[SHIROE] RIGHT.
WE COULD HAVE MADE ALL
THE PROMISES WE WANTED TO
BACK AT THE CASTLE,
AND NO ONE IN AKIHABARA WOULD
HAVE GONE ALONG WITH IT.
SHE UNDERSTOOD THAT
WE'RE ALL FREE.
SO TO WIN THEM OVER
AND CONVINCE THEM,
SHE MIGHT HAVE TO
SPEAK TO EACH ONE.
BUT, YEAH, SHE REALLY
SEEMS TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH US.
AND SHE KNOWS SHE HAS TO BE
RESPECTFUL WHEN SHE ASKS
FOR OUR HELP.
[AKATSUKI] OH, RIGHT. BUT
WOULDN'T THAT BE A BIT OBVIOUS?
[SHIROE] YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
IN FACT, IT'S SO OBVIOUS THAT
WE ALMOST FORGOT ABOUT IT
WHEN WE WERE AT THE TABLE
DEMANDING RESPECT.
WE ALMOST BLEW IT.
(WHIMPERING)
[RAYNESHIA] WHAT ARE
THOSE LIGHTS?
[KRUSTY] THAT'S AKIHABARA.
[RAYNESHIA] IT'S NIGHT.
THE LIGHT IS SO WARM.
(GRIFFIN CRIES)
(RAYNESHIA SCREAMS)
[SHIROE, VOICE‐OVER]
IMAGINE HOW AMAZING IT'D
BE IF SHE WAS THE ONE
WHO ENDS UP SAVING THE
FREEDOM CITIES OF EASTAL
FROM THE RUT THEY'RE STUCK IN.
THAT LAZY, COWARDLY PRINCESS.
[AKATSUKI, VOICE‐OVER]
SHE FINDS HERSELF IN
A TOWN SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WITH THINGS SHE'S NEVER SEEN,
THINGS SHE'S NEVER HEARD,
AND PEOPLE SHE'S NEVER MET.
SHE LEARNS HOW BIG THE WORLD
IS AND HOW TINY SHE IS.
SHE CRIES OUT WITH ALL HER
RESOLVE AND HER HOPE,
AND HER WORDS DRIVE THE
ADVENTURERS TO ACTION,
NEXT TIME ON "LOG HORIZON."
[SHIROE] ALWAYS LOOK
30 SECONDS AHEAD.