[birds chirping]
[TOR]
So hot.
I can't breathe.
Suffocating.
They're so soft.
Wait, what are?
Tor, a little more
gently there, please.
[gasps]
Wait, Lilith?
What's she doing here?
What the hell? Julie?
Your hands are so warm.
Please don't move them.
[TOR screaming]
Good morning, Tor, what
seems to be the problem?
You act like you've never
seen a nude woman before.
That's just it!
Why are you both naked?
[yawns]
I find it too
uncomfortable to get
a good night's sleep in clothes.
And as for me,
it just got really
hot last night.
Look, just please get
dressed now, okay?
[TOMOE]
Morning!
Ugh!
Rise and shine, Tor.
That goes for you, too, Julie.
We've got a lot of
training to day.
[TOMOE]
Tor, you're a perv!
And a dog!
--[birds chirping]
--[waves crashing]
[groans]
Man, what a crazy
way to start the day.
[TOMOE]
Stay right there, Tor!
Tomoe?
I beg your forgiveness!
Julie and Lilith
explained everything.
It was rude of me to
jump to conclusions again!
Look, I'm really glad they
set you straight and all.
But I'm begging you.
Please stop bowing like that.
[TOMOE]
As I've said to you before,
I feel like this is the only
way to set things right!
I see you've wasted no time
getting up to your old tricks.
[TATSU grunting]
What on earth did you do, Tor?
It's...
my fault.
Lilith and I were nude--
TMI, Julie!
Um, hey, guys.
Maybe we should get
our swimming exercises in
before Miss Tsukimi comes
down here and gets mad.
Oh no, we don't want that.
[TORA]
Hmm. Agreed.
I don't want to
get punished by that
black-hearted bunny, either.
[IMARI] Wait a minute,
you mean you guys
don't like Professor Bunbun?
But why? She's so cute.
[giggles]
I guess ignorance
really is bliss, isn't it?
Miyabi.
Thanks a lot for bailing
me out back there.
[MIYABI]
I had no idea.
I never knew it before.
That falling in love
could be as thrilling as this.
Make you feel warm
inside and out.
Fill you with strength,
give you a purpose.
And somehow,
even make the
entire world sparkle.
[RITO] And that
concludes our schedule
for training camp, class!
As a reward for all
of your hard work,
our last day tomorrow
will be nothing but
much-deserved free time!
But don't get too
crazy, or you'll make
one bothered bunny, understand?
[STUDENTS]
Yes, ma'am!
Tor!
After that workout, I'm filthy,
so I'm going to take a bath
and clean myself for you.
Would you care to join me?
Join you?
Nej. He won't, but I will.
Tor, I'm going to
take a bath, too.
Hey, wait, what's the big idea?
I don't recall inviting you.
Maybe those
two're hitting it off.
You think?
I dunno.
But I'm off for a
little soak myself.
Well. We got through camp.
We sure did, Miyabi.
And hey, you did really
great this week.
Oh, thanks.
But, the only reason I did
was because of you.
Hmm?
Um, nothing!
Oh, hey, I thought I'd ask,
do you have any
plans for tomorrow yet?
No, nothing special at least.
Well, in that case,
would you want to come
have fun with us tomorrow?
Me, Tomoe, and Imari, I mean.
We'd love to have you.
But of course,
that's only if you
want to come, that is.
Yeah, thanks, I would!
But where?
This place is pretty rugged
so what did you have
in mind exactly?
Well. The place behind you.
Huh?
Wow, there's a gorgeous
beach right in front of me
and I totally miss it.
Am I a complete dufus or what?
Uh.
[giggles]
[TOR] By laughing, I
guess that's a yes, huh?
[MIYABI] Will you hold it
against me if I said it was?
[BOTH laugh]
Yow!
Hot, hot, hot!
How am I the only guy here?
I can't believe it.
Tora's taking a nap
and Tatsu's off communing
with the god of muscle.
Who is the god of
muscle, anyway?
I'm sorry to keep
you waiting, Tor.
Well, what do you think?
Oh, you mean how
you look in that?
You're cute.
Really cute, Julie.
Ja.
And what about us, Tor?
Hi there, big boy!
[giggling]
I'm sure that you're dazzled by
the veritable feast before you,
but what do you think?
Would you care to weigh
in on how we all look?
Uh, well.
Okay.
In your particular case, Lilith.
I think the word "gorgeous"
suits you to a tee.
And Imari.
I think you've got a
really incredible figure.
Uh, I mean, athletically
speaking, of course!
Tomoe.
Well, you're beautiful.
Hey. Your face is all red.
You're not getting
sunburned, are you?
Miyabi.
Hey, what's the big idea?
C'mon, take that frumpy
thing off already, would ya?
Thanks, but to be honest,
my swimsuit doesn't
look very good on me.
Plus, I'm a little shy.
There's no use arguing!
Hai-yah!
[screaming]
Ah!
[MIYABI whimpering]
Oh. Hi, there, Tor.
Uh, hi, there yourself,
"Mi-boobie,"
no, wait, I mean Miyabi!
You look nice.
Yeah. Great, in fact.
Oh! You think so, Tor?
Why thank you.
[LILITH giggles]
Well, Tor, I have to say
you're a pretty good
beauty contest judge.
[TOMOE] Yep. Now
let's get going, 'kay?
[IMARI] Right, the ocean
awaits, so come on!
[ALL giggling]
[IMARI] Yahoo!
Actually, a dip right
now sounds like fun.
Kick!
Hey, what was that for?
For neglecting me the way that
you did, you insensitive ape,
since you told all those
other girls how they looked
but not me!
So how do you like
me in beach mode?
Tell me what you
really think, okay?
Your beach mode seems to be
the same as your bitch mode.
Oh, yeah?
So then tell me.
Do you think I'm
any more violent in
beach mode, you
rotten little brat?
[TOR]
You're cutting off my air!
[RITO]
Well? Huh?
[laughing]
Wow, those two sure
are close, huh?
I guess.
It must be nice.
Miyabi.
[TOR] Yep, the beach
was definitely
a good place to have fun.
Um.
Hi there, Tor.
Hey, do you think
you'd want to
swim with me?
Oh no!
Julie!
I told you not to go out alone!
Hey, look at this, Tor!
Thanks to you, I can swim
forward all by myself now.
I see.
Nice job, Juli--
Are you okay?
[JULIE coughing]
--Ja, I'm fine, thanks.
--[TOR screaming]
Julie? Up top! Look!
Hmm?
Looks nice and sunny.
No, your swimsuit!
Did you see anything?
I did, but just barely.
Well, I guess "just barely"
is okay then.
But let's go get my
top back, all right?
Ah!
Wait.
Julie. Let go, would ya?
Nej, Tor.
I can't do that right now.
If I let go, then you
might get a peek.
Look.
My top's right there.
And what goes in it
is right against my back.
Oh, help me, Tor!
Look, I'm drowning!
Hey, come on now!
I know that you
know how to swim!
Yes, but not when I'm
drowning in your love!
[TOR]
Oh. You are not!
Knock it off, 'kay, and would
you please let go of me?
Hah!
If you're getting
cold feet, Irregular,
put some more
backbone into it, would ya?
Are these guys always like this?
Yes, they usually
are, unfortunately.
Good grief.
By the way,
have you noticed anything
about Miyabi lately?
[TOMOE]
Yeah. I sure have.
She'd been down on
herself for a while.
But now it seems like
she's recovered.
I'm glad. Is that what you mean?
Yeah.
We'll be saying
goodbye tomorrow.
I guess a little
meddling can't hurt.
[TOR sighs]
Mmm, this is so nice.
Talk about relaxing.
The branch school
is lucky to have
a hidden gem like this place.
[MIYABI]
Wait, Miss Tsukimi!
No, don't!
Stop! Please don't
grab them like that!
[RITO]
Oh, wow!
One touch is all it takes!
Look at how these
bazongas bounce!
[laughing]
[MIYABI] No!
[LILITH] I must admit you have
two amazing attributes there.
[MIYABI protesting]
[LILITH] In terms of bust size,
I know when I've been defeated,
therefore I concede to you.
[RITO] What's your
bra size, Miyabi?
[gasps]
[MIYABI]
I'm not telling you that!
[RITO]
You better tell me!
[MIYABI]
Ah! Hey, no pinching!
"Pinching"?
[RITO] Or this'll keep
happening until you do!
Pinchy-pinch!
[MIYABI screaming]
[MIYABI] I'll tell, I'll tell,
just please stop!
It's an F!
I wear an F!
Miyabi's an "F" for
"Fantasy Size?"
[MIYABI]
Ah! Stop!
They're not cantaloupes--
[LILITH] It's rare
I'm ever intimidated.
But now I guess I'll have to
consider her a real rival.
Oh, my, what a
strange phenomenon!
These are so soft
and supple, but these
little bits here
just got real hard!
No, please knock it off, okay?
--Pinchy pinchy pinchy--
--[MIYABI] No more!
I'm begging you to stop!
[TOMOE]
That's enough!
If you really insist on
groping somebody's bosom,
then let it be mine
instead, Miss Tsukimi!
Oh, so then you're
volunteering for
my little squeeze test, are you?
--[TOMOE screaming]
--[RITO laughing]
[TOMOE]
Miss Tsukimi?
Ooh, this pair is worthy, too!
And her.
We're both about
the same size I'd say.
No, don't! Please stop this now!
Julie, you've gotta save me!
But I'm curious about them, too.
[TOMOE]
No, not you, too!
[TOMOE screaming]
These remind me a lot of Mama.
You okay, Miyabi?
Uh-huh. 'Least now I am.
[JULIE]
They're soft.
[IMARI]
Hey, tell me something.
[distant screams]
[IMARI]
You like Tor, don't you?
[MIYABI]
Yeah.
Hey, wait a minute, you mean
that you can actually tell?
But how did you know?
Well, that's easy.
You haven't been able to
take your eyes off of him
since you got here.
[whimpers]
You've got some serious
competition for him.
That's true.
[IMARI]
There's the passionate Lilith,
the friendly Tomoe,
and even the filter-less
Professor Bunbun.
Then of course there's Tor's
Duo partner and roommate,
the exotic Julie.
I'd say she's your
biggest foe of all.
[MIYABI]
I know.
She's genuine, cute,
and incredibly strong.
So I don't stand a
chance against her.
[IMARI]
To be honest,
I really can't see
those two as a couple.
They seem to be more
like parent and child.
Or maybe even a
master and his dog.
C'mon.
Then again- you have
got a point there.
You know, I've seen you
looking at Tor a lot yourself.
Hmm?
Um, You okay?
[laughs]
We both clicked
when we first met.
It was right before
the opening ceremony.
I figured that we'd end up
seeing a lot of each other.
And maybe even become
more than just good friends.
Except that
I failed the Screening Rite and
ended up here far away from him.
And that's the reason why I
want you to go for it, Miyabi.
So that you won't
have any regrets. 'Kay?
You're really sure?
[IMARI]
Go for it!
[MIYABI]
I will!
[violin playing]
[MIYABI] So how
exactly do I do this?
How do I get Tor to notice me?
[screams]
Huh?
[MIYABI]
Ow!
[TOMOE]
Are you all right, Miyabi?
Uh-huh.
I think I just twisted it.
I wouldn't be so
sure about that!
In fact, you better
not walk on it until
you've gotten it checked out!
In the meantime, why don't
you just let Tor carry you?
But I'm not that hurt!
No, Imari's right.
Well, then, hop on.
[giggles]
Uh, okay.
Thanks so much, Tor.
[IMARI] Wow, will you
look at the time!
We better hurry back
because we're on
chow duty tonight, guys!
We are? This is the
first I've heard of it.
Oh, I must have forgot to tell
you they asked if we'd help out!
Well, it's almost dinner time,
so we better get a
move on and quickly, too.
[IMARI]
Tor, Miyabi,
we're gonna go on ahead, okay?
Oh, Lilith, Professor Bunbun,
you're both on kitchen
duty as well.
Hah!
Seeing those brats all
buddy-buddy the way they
really chafes my cheeks!
Wouldn't you agree, Miss Priss?
No, because everybody
gets a chance, I guess.
Not that anyone
else will win, though.
What was that about?
[TOR]
Hey, you know what?
This isn't the first time
you and I have done this.
I also carried you
after you collapsed
on the track, remember?
[MIYABI]
That's right, you did.
You even said some
words of encouragement
to me that day, and I can't tell
you how much I appreciated them.
They really brightened my day.
[TOR laughing] If that's all it
takes to cheer you up
I'll say anything you like.
Oh, you would?
Well, there is something I'd
like to hear you say to me.
And that's my name.
I know, that sounds weird but,
I'd like to hear you say it.
I'm sure Julie and Lilith
like hearing theirs.
So, will you, please, Tor?
Sure, of course.
I'd be happy to do
that for you, Miyabi.
[MIYABI]
Wow.
Thanks, Tor.
That means so much to me.
[TOR]
Oh, sure. Um, you're welcome.
[distant waves crashing]
[BOTH gasp]
[MIYABI]
How beautiful.
[TOR]
Yeah.
It's breathtaking.
Tor, I think I'd like to
walk on my own now.
You sure your foot can take it?
It seems to have gotten
a whole lot better.
Well, all right then.
Just don't overdo it, 'kay?
[MIYABI]
Tor. Wait.
[TOR]
What's up?
[MIYABI]
I want to thank you,
for everything.
'Cause, you know. If it
wasn't for your help.
I wouldn't be here now.
You've really made an
impression on me.
I have?
That's right.
So much.
That, I also...
Well, you see
the thing is, Tor...
I like you.
I really like you.
I have to admit
those outdoor baths
are quite relaxing and
aren't bad at all.
So you mean you're actually
enjoying student life.
What strange turn
of events led to this?
If my time at school leads to
me achieving Absolute Duo,
then I don't see any reason why
I shouldn't enjoy the ride.
Correct?
[ping]
Seven people brought together
with Absolute Duo at their core.
You're a member of Reign.
You don't need me
to explain that.
Do you, Blaze Diabolica?
Don't bandy that name about.
Or I'll make you
regret it if you do.
[LILITH] You're rather cold
to somebody who's
currently in Reign's sights.
[sighs]
That older gentleman
must be in quite a bind.
I'm sure that he is.
And in fact,
he'll probably try
something tonight.
Well, if you're mistaken,
then it appears that
my coming here
will have all been for nothing.
I see, so then you're the bait?
[SAKUYA]
Yes.
Just like these branch school
students that I've prepared
to serve as
sacrifices if need be.
Tor Kokonoe.
He even thanked me for giving
all those students another shot.
Not knowing my true
intentions for them, of course.
Hmph.
Miyabi.
I'm sure it seems kinda sudden.
You and I haven't known
each other for very long,
but you've always cheered me on
in the short time that we have.
Your kind words have
given me so much
support and encouragement
that actually--
I love you!
Do you feel the same way?
If you do,
then would you please
be my boyfriend, Tor?
[TOR thinking]
Miyabi,
is in love with me?
But...
these hands of mine.
[gasps]
[breath quivering]
[YOUNG BOY]
Oh, Tor.
Another one dead
because you're too weak.
[TOR gasps]
[TOR]
I'm sorry.
But I can't do that, Miyabi.
[gasps]
[TOR]
You see.
I'm weak.
That's why I can't.
Oh okay.
Um. Yeah sure,
that's no problem.
I understand, and I'm also
stupid.
I should have just kept quiet!
[cries]
I'm sorry!
[TOR]
No, wait.
[explosion]
[gasps]
What the?
--[gunshots]
--[screaming]
[K]
Now, then, shall we begin?
The Rebels, our
god-slaying corps
and the Exceeds.
It's time to judge and
be judged in the Selection!
It's those armored guys
who butted in on our Survive.
I never thought
we'd see them again.
Tomoe. They seem tougher
than they were before.
That's not a problem
'cause so are we!
Let's go!
[JULIE]
Next time: "Rebels."
Miyabi. Please be all right!