I got her!
[gasps]
[screams]
Damn, our sneak attack
is a bust!
Then let's rush her!
Now!
[running footsteps]
[shouting]
Hmph.
[grunting]
Why, hello there, Tor.
Lilith.
Now then,
let us dance.
To the accompaniment
of clashing shields
and smoking guns.
I really didn't think
we'd encounter one another
so soon, Tor.
But I'm so
pleasantly surprised.
Let's make this quick.
Um, hold on.
Can I say something first?
What is it?
Well?
When you initially asked
to be Duo partners,
I never apologized to you
for turning you down.
I'm sorry.
But why bring it up now?
Do you think by doing that
I'll somehow go
a little bit easier on you?
No, and in fact,
I hope you don't.
I want to fight you
at full strength.
What?
If we fight each other
at full power,
then we'll understand each other
better afterwards.
That'll help us become friends.
Don't you think so?
I think you might be
an idiot, Tor.
You know, sometimes
I think the same thing.
But this seems to be
the only way
that we can do this.
Huh. Well, all right.
But I do wonder
if you're going to be able
to keep up with me
at full power.
Quit breaking things!
Think of the shopkeepers!
Oh, relax.
I'll reimburse them
so they can get it fixed up
as good as new.
[grunts]
It's nuts you rented out
the A La Mode Mall
for your Survive Dance Party.
Oh, come on, admit it,
this is fun.
A whole lot more
than being stuck
in a stuffy old classroom.
Right?
So it's manageable
from this distance, huh?
Oh, wow.
So you're calculating
the trajectory
from the angle
of the barrel?
--Well done.
--Oh, yeah?
Well, you still haven't seen
nothing yet!
[shouts]
[shouting]
Take her down,
you guys!
[TOR thinking]
Julie? She's early!
[LILITH thinking]
Hm.
They're using a decoy
and an ambush
to force me to dodge
to a very specific point.
One where your best fighter
will finish me off, eh?
Someone put this together well.
But still.
[LILITH] You need to put
just a little more thought
into an Exceed's
physical capabilities.
If Julie's timing
hadn't been slightly off,
I might have found myself
in a spot of trouble.
Now listen up, Tor.
You really amuse me
a great deal.
That's why I'm saving
you for last as my main course.
[LILITH chuckles]
[gasps]
[MIYABI yelps]
Ow, that hurt.
Are you okay, Miyabi?
I'll be all right, Tor.
But thank you for asking.
[yelps]
Did you see anything?
No, I sure didn't,
so you can rest easy, okay?
[gunshot]
[TOR]
Lilith.
We better work out
our next move, guys.
And quickly, too.
[TOMOE]
From the sound of things,
Lilith is fighting
in the Sky Court up ahead.
That means we can
either go after her now
or wait and intercept her
when she arrives here.
I say we go after her.
You won't hear
an objection from me.
[TATSU grunts]
Um, then I'm in
if you guys are!
Uh.
[TOR]
Something wrong, Julie?
Nej, and I agree
with the group's decision.
[TOR]
Oh, okay.
All right, it's settled then.
There are two routes
into the Sky Court.
Tor, you, Tatsu, and Julie
will take the main route.
The rest of us
will take the long way,
and hopefully we can attack her
from both sides.
Tor.
She took everyone out already.
Dammit.
[TOR thinking]
Lilith, where are you?
[grunts, groans]
Tatsu!
As an avid hunter,
I'm quite skilled at camouflage.
[shouting]
Come on, don't you remember
you're tonight's main course?
So, be a good boy
and wait already.
I'm real sorry,
but I can't stand waiting.
Well, I can't stand
a man who's impatient!
[TOR thinking]
She's gonna shoot me this close?
Crap!
We'll take the rest
nice and slow
after I've eliminated
all the others, okay?
Julie, no!
We need to wait
for Tomoe's group!
Nej, it's all right, Tor!
Ah, an all-too
predictable move.
Oh!
I'm so very disappointed
in you, Julie.
I expected you to put up
a much bigger fight.
Julie!
So much for standing
by her always.
Not so fast!
Let's go! Move!
Right! Gotcha!
[TORA]
She's not coming after us? Huh.
I guess she was serious
about leaving Tor
for last then, wasn't she?
[TOMOE groans]
Tomoe, did you get hit?
[JULIE]
Oh, no, what is that?
This? Don't fret.
It's nothing.
[TOMOE]
Forget me.
What about that
shoulder of yours?
[MIYABI]
Tomoe!
I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
Hey, we're friends.
You would have done
the same for me.
Yes, but--
You've really been rushing
into things today.
[TOMOE]
Is something going on, Julie?
Nej. Nothing, I swear.
[TOMOE]
All right.
But please remember this.
Your Blaze has a lot to do
with speed
and keeping a cool head
to find the right moment
to use it.
Ja.
'Kay.
So how do you guys propose
we take Lilith down?
It looks like
we'll have to wait
for our chance
at close combat, I suppose.
But we're not as strong
as we were
and Tomoe's hurt.
Plus, Julie's got
a slight injury as well.
And Miyabi's lance is
so ginormous and awkward.
She can't get very close.
Yeah.
We've all got our own strengths
and weaknesses here.
But in terms of raw,
destructive power,
Miyabi's got us all beat,
and I think
she is our best shot.
Do you think so?
Heh. Yeah, but Lilith
is a real sneaky fighter.
And not only that,
but she's cocky too.
She's such a pain!
Cocky? Wait a sec.
Yeah, that might be the answer.
Maybe.
What is it you're
mumbling about, Tor?
Hmm.
--[footsteps]
--Huh?
--Tor.
--Julie?
Hold on, why aren't you waiting
at your assigned position?
I'm sorry, but I have
to talk to you now, Tor.
It'll only take
a second, okay?
All right, what's going on?
Tomoe was right.
I have been
rushing into everything.
Is it because of that
Duo stuff with Lilith?
[JULIE] I know you said
that you turned her down, Tor,
but even so.
I'm worried about
what might happen
if she does well in this Survive
and really impresses you.
I get it now.
So all this time, you thought...
[JULIE whimpers]
[TOR]
I want to protect you, Julie,
and be the one that
you can rely on, remember?
Oh, Tor.
Listen, there's no reason
to worry, okay?
You.
You're my only Duo partner.
I mean that.
Got it?
Ja.
[LILITH]
Did you two forget the theme
of this dance party is
"Survive," not "Talk"?
[TOR] That was some
nice shooting, Lilith.
I had no idea that
you were even up there.
[LILITH] Blending in with your
environment is Hunting 101.
That and bagging your prey,
of course, so...
Isn't it about time
we wrapped this thing up?
Oh, and I can see your
friend hiding over there.
Huh. Didn't I tell you guys
she was a real pain?
Where's the rest?
I know that
I wounded one of you.
And the other one
is pretty slow.
Did you leave those two
behind somewhere?
Nej, we would never do a thing
like that to Tomoe and Miyabi.
That's an admirable
trait to possess,
and I do respect that you
look after your teammates.
But nevertheless.
[LILITH]
Let's end this, shall we?
And now, it's time for
the last dance, my darlings!
[grunting]
That strike had a lot
more feeling to it, Julie!
But it appears
my previous attack
did some
lasting damage to you
because you're too slow!
[JULIE whimpering]
Blaze on!
Wow, nicely done!
Hey, over here, I hope you
haven't forgotten about me!
Oh, don't you worry!
I haven't!
Then do your worst!
Oh!
This isn't over yet!
--Dammit, no!
--Tor!
Don't worry about me, guys!
We're taking her down
just like we planned!
In the shape you're in?
I doubt it, Tor.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I've finally got you
right where I want you!
Mjolnir!
[shouting]
That's impressive!
But still not enough!
[shouting]
I will not be defeated!
She hasn't cocked!
Do it now!
Ja!
This dance is over, Lilith!
Oh, the only one
it's over for is you.
Oh!
[gunshot]
Julie.
This is such a pity.
It was a fake-out.
Wow, so you guys really thought
that I have to cock my rifle
every time I shoot it?
[chuckles]
[TOR] No, but it is what
we wanted you to believe.
What?
Tora had you pegged.
You're so "cocky," you just
revealed the truth to us!
That makes this checkmate,
Lilith.
But how? I'm positive I shot you
right through the chest.
So that's the reason
you were moving so slowly.
You were both
fighting together.
Huh, I get it.
There were two of you
waiting in ambush.
[TOR] You almost had me
at first, Lilith.
But then I remembered--
you never reloaded once
that time at the mall.
Ah. Nothing gets
past you, does it, Tor?
It's over.
So just give up, okay?
And surrender to us now.
[LILITH]
Don't say it again!
I won't give up, not now
and not ever, you hear me?
[ALL gasping]
[JULIE]
Tor!
That isn't from her Blaze.
It's a real bullet!
[MAN] He got close, didn't he?
Lilith Bristol.
Who are they?
Do you know, Lilith?
Not at all!
Who are you people?
And just what is it
that you want?
We come bearing an invitation
for you, Miss Bristol,
and it's from none other
than Equipment Smith,
the Master Armorer.
That should suffice.
Well, does it?
Oh.
Yes, it does, quite.
And I thank you very much.
But you can tell him
that I refuse!
And I won't accept anything
from someone rude enough
to interrupt my dance party!
[gunshot]
Sorry about that.
We're to bring you in, even if
it means getting a little rough.
So now you're coming with us.
Like hell she is!
[shouting]
[TORA]
What the hell?
I know we're exhausted,
but still.
Our attacks,
they didn't do anything.
It's because Exceeds
aren't the only ones
who've surpassed humanity.
That's the reason.
[scream]
[K]
You be still now.
It would be a real shame
if you were to make
my trigger finger slip,
wouldn't it?
[LILITH]
Let her go!
I'll accept the invitation.
But only if you
release her right now!
[K]
You have my thanks.
Now I'm going to be able to
show my face to the bossman.
We're leaving this place now
so follow me
and don't try anything.
Lilith, I--
I'm sorry we couldn't
finish things properly, Tor.
It's been fun, though.
[crying]
[TORA]
Damn it.
Just who the hell were
those creeps, anyway?
[TOR]
That doesn't matter, Tora!
The only thing
that does is Lilith!
Ja.
Huh, isn't that just like you?
[crying]
Tor, I'm so sorry about this.
Hey, don't worry,
we're gonna get Lilith back.
And when we do that--
you greet us
with a smile, okay?
[crying]
Uh-huh.
[LILITH]
What are you doing here?
My question exactly.
I'm here to get Lilith back,
why else?
[LILITH]
Stand down, Tor!
You're in
no condition to fight.
Do you have a death wish?
[TOR]
No, but it's like you said.
I want to finish things properly
between you and me.
I won't say it again,
you mule-headed idiot!
Well, the same goes for me,
Lilith!
C'mon,
we're at full strength!
We've gotta fight so we can
better understand each other!
This is such a childish game.
Would you gentlemen end it
since we're on a schedule here?
--No!
--[gunfire]
[TOR] I've gotta put
the last of my strength
into one single blow!
And then... Shatter!
You must be getting desperate.
You don't get it, do you?
Don't you know
where we are?
[K]
No!
[loud rumbling]
[TOR]
Lilith!
[LILITH]
You've got me, Tor.
Julie! Tora!
--[JULIE] Ja!
--[TORA] We got this!
[rumbling continues]
[K]
To resort to such a tactic!
Lend me your strength, Lilith.
We can do this.
Right, Blaze on!
Here we go, Tor!
But you pull the trigger!
It's over for you, buddy!
[TOR] Um, you're
really sure about this?
[LILITH]
Of course.
You want to fight
with me at my full power
so we can understand
each other better, right?
Yeah, but after everything
that happened today,
I'm pretty beat up.
Well, I've hurt my arm,
so in my book,
I'd say that makes us even.
All right then.
If you're willing, I won't
object to settling this thing
--once and for all!
--Atta boy, Tor!
[grunts]
Hmm.
[shouting]
Sir, my apologies.
The Unit got a little
scuffed up during this op.
[MASTER ARMORER]
It's no matter,
the adjustments
have yet to be made anyway.
Besides,
the data you got is plenty.
What shall we do
about Lilith Bristol,
the so-called Exception?
[MASTER ARMORER]
She's an intriguing subject,
but there's no need
to go overboard.
After all,
the one I'm really after is--
[K] Yes, the witch
who's pulling the strings,
Blaze Diabolica.
You know, I half expected
she'd show her face here today.
[MASTER ARMORER]
She's keeping herself guarded.
Speaking of the lady
in question, tell me,
how are those Exceeds
she made, anyway?
[K]
The Exceeds?
Hey, help me! Please!
Well, sir, I think that
they'll be quite amusing.
[gunshot]
I'm so bored. Ugh!
I so wish
I could start moving again.
Nej. The doctor said
you have to stay in bed.
Listen to Julie,
Tor, she's right.
She certainly is. Fighting
with Lilith was reckless.
[grunt]
--[knocking]
--[TOR] Come in.
[TOR]
Uh, hi, Lilith.
[TORA] Huh,
what do you doing here?
It's only natural to visit
an injured friend, isn't it?
--Huh?
--[ALL] You're friends?
Aren't we, Tor?
Don't you remember?
You said we'd be friends
after we fought at full power!
Oh, and I also
wanted to come here
because you came to rescue me.
So, um,
thank you, Tor.
[TOR]
Sure.
[LILITH]
I also wanted to say I'm sorry
for slapping you at
the theme park the other night.
I bet that hurt.
Eh, I've survived worse.
Good to know.
And to all of you, I'm sorry
for not taking you seriously.
No prob.
It actually turned out to be
a pretty good experience
for every one of us.
--Hmm.
--[grunts]
I came here
for one more reason.
Is that other thing
still a no-go, Tor?
Yeah, I'm sorry, but I've
already got a Duo partner
that I'm committed to.
Very well.
But if you should
ever change your mind,
you'll tell me, won't you?
Tor is my Duo partner!
But of course!
Oh, I almost forgot!
There's one more important
thing that I need to tell you.
Now I won't say it again.
So please listen closely.
[BOTH]
Aah!
I've decided this.
You, Tor Kokonoe,
will be my future husband.
[ALL]
What?
Tor, does this mean
that you two have been--?
Oh, Tor, how could
you do such a thing?
Don't you have any shame,
you perverted dog?
You've got it wrong!
All of you!
Right.
[TOR]
Don't leave, Lilith, tell 'em!
I'll tell them this--
I'm serious about winning
Tor's heart and I'll do it!
Just you wait!
I'm not giving up on becoming
Tor's Duo partner, Julie.
Nej.
Tor's partner is--
Fine, then I
won't give up, either!
--What?
--Okay, I won't give up, either!
[gasping]
[JULIE] Next time,
"Silver-Blonde, Yellow Topaz."
Well, I won't give up, either!
[GIRLS]
What?