[RITO]
Good morning!
I'm so very excited that all of
you have worked out your Duos.
From now on, you'll be
sitting in your Duos, too.
You could even think of it
as sort of a new beginning.
Although, I can already see that
some of you have decided
to stay in the exact
same seats as before.
Yeah. The two of us
fit together nicely.
[STUDENTS snickering]
Whoa, hang on!
She's talking about
our personalities!
Well, now that all of your Duos
have been officially decided,
it's just about time for us
to go ahead and move on
to the much anticipated
mock Blaze battle.
Your first Novgladius!
You might be wondering
how all of this will work.
Well, each and
every one of you,
will fight everyone else!
[laughs sinisterly]
--[birds chirping]
--[swords clanging]
Ah!
Yaaah!
And that's checkmate.
You got me.
That makes four losses in a row.
[sighs]
You know, to be honest,
the way you move is
a little bit awkward.
I haven't really gotten used to
fighting with this shield yet.
But you'll get better.
Yeah, but the problem is the
Novgladius is next Saturday.
Right now, there's no way
I'll be up to snuff.
I've got an idea.
Hmm?
It's about how to use
your shield.
I want you to try to punch me.
Okay. I'll try.
[JULIE]
I! Two!
That's too close for it to work!
That was one step
too close, huh?
Try it from here then.
On "I," step forward while
blocking your opponent's attack.
And on "two,"
strike with Mjolnir.
What is "Mjolnir"?
I hope it doesn't bother
you, but that's the name
I've given to your right fist.
Mjolnir is the most
powerful weapon
wielded by
the thunder god, Thor.
[TOR thinking] Now she's
coming up with pet names?
So, what do you think?
I think you've got a
pretty excellent idea there.
Haaaaaah!
The thing is, this
attack isn't a Blaze,
so if it connects with anyone,
it'll hurt 'em for real.
That's why I don't want
to use it unless I have to.
Oh, I see.
All of that stuff aside,
I think this new way of using
my shield will totally work.
Would you mind practicing
with me for a little while?
Nej.
Hmm?
I... I made it!
[gasps]
Hey, Miyabi!
Wait a minute.
Where am I?
Well, look who
decided to wake up.
Oh, hey, Tor. What's up?
[gasps]
Hang on, wait. What the heck
are you carrying me for?
Stop! I'm getting down
whether you like it or not,
so let me go!
Would you calm down
before you hurt yourself!
Not to mention
you're rubbing on me.
I'm what?
Everything'll be fine,
just stop freaking out!
[MIYABI screaming]
Are you feeling better?
Uh. A little.
But why did you...
You know?
You collapsed on the track.
You don't remember?
No.
Are you telling me
that you came to my rescue?
More or less.
Why don't we get you
to the infirmary,
just to be on the safe side.
Right. Thank you, Tor.
It's good to try hard,
just not too hard.
[MIYABI sighs]
[TOR]
What is it?
[MIYABI] If I don't push
myself to the limit,
then I'll just hold Tomoe back.
[sighs]
My main problem is
that I'm not particularly
good at anything.
In fact, I'm terrible
at both schoolwork
and physical training.
You see, when I learned
I was suited for a Lukifer,
I was so thrilled.
It was great.
It was like I finally had
my chance to be special.
But then...
I met Tomoe, and Julie
and you, Tor.
Now that I'm around
all these amazing people,
I'm back to feeling like I've
got absolutely nothing to offer.
So you ran until you
collapsed on the track?
What else could I do?
I've gotta get better.
Physical activity is
is the most important part
of getting stronger.
So running's not
a bad idea at all.
Wha? Really?
Talent doesn't mean
anything unless you've spent
enough time
working on the basics.
So if you don't give up
on the running,
you're sure to get stronger.
But try not to overdo it
next time, 'kay?
[laughs]
Okay.
Thank you for all
of your help, Tor.
[inaudible]
[TOR screaming]
[gasping]
[panting]
[gasps]
Tor?
[RITO] Now then, let's review
the Novgladius rules!
It lasts for two hours,
from 5 to 7 p.m.,
and will happen at the north
end of the school grounds!
You'll be fighting
face-to-face,
drawing on your Blaze's
unique qualities,
as well as doing
anything else you can
to try and gain the upper hand!
Best of luck to everyone!
It's time to do this. Let's go.
About our plan...
Are you sure it's going to work?
Of course.
Just keep moving ahead.
Knock down whoever's there.
We'll keep this very simple.
You know, we really
do fit together nicely.
[RITO]
Okay, here we go!
Let the Novgladius begin!
[clock tower chiming]
Okay, you ready?
I am.
[BOTH]
Blaze on!
Aaa-yah!
What? No way!
Hyaaah!
[grunts]
Owie.
[gasps]
Wait! I give up!
Looks like our first
win of the day.
Yeah.
[BOTH giggling]
Uh...
[TOR chuckles awkwardly]
[BOTH shrieking]
Sneak attacks, mimicry,
and old-fashioned seduction.
I guess everyone has
their own tactics.
Yeah.
[TOR]
One hour left.
With so many Duos
out of the competition,
it'll be harder to find
who we fight next.
Why don't we go somewhere
we haven't been yet?
Ah. Do you mean?
Yah!
We've got to be careful.
It's clear that we're
now in striking distance.
[bells jingling]
Well, hello to you, too!
Tomoe.
[chuckles]
I figured that you were too
good for such a simple attack.
I've gotta say, I've really
been looking forward
to taking you two on.
And we feel
the same way about you.
Well, then...
Tachibana-Style Eighteen Arts!
Tomoe Tachibana.
Attack!
Hah!
What else is up her sleeve?
The Tachibana School covers
a variety of martial arts.
You should know,
this and judo
are my specialties.
So, shall we begin?
Try and block my
Tachibana Oro-chi Form!
Do your thing, Miyabi!
Blaze on!
All right, guys.
Prepare yourselves. Ah!
[screaming]
You've got me to deal with, too!
Tor, you cover
the back. Got it?
Yeah, no problem, partner!
Come on!
Please don't take
this personally, Tor!
[MIYABI screaming]
[grunting]
[TOR screaming]
[panting and whimpering]
I can't keep going like this!
[grunts]
I knew it.
I'm just not strong enough.
[TOR]
I'm impressed.
Huh?
Pushing me back
the way that you did.
That's pretty incredible.
Nice job.
Yeah? You really think so?
I do.
There's no letting my
guard down around you now.
And I'll have to train harder.
I will, too!
Just you wait, you'll see!
I'll get stronger and
stronger till I can--
[sighs]
That's right.
We'll both work hard.
Sound good?
Huh? Mm.
So this is you
with your gloves off.
You're good, but I refuse
to lose this fight!
It's not over!
And that's checkmate.
Did you actually see
that last attack
that came from behind you?
Yeah.
I know that you're
very powerful,
so I have to stay
as alert as I can.
You win this round, Julie.
We both did our best.
Yeah. We sure did!
The Novgladius isn't
quite over yet.
Looks like we have enough
time for one more match.
I'd like a go at Tora
and his partner.
[distant screaming]
Tora!
Tatsu!
Are you both okay?
[WOMAN]
Mr. Kokonoe.
Oh, Miss Tsukimi!
What in the world
happened to these two guys?
I don't know. We just
got here ourselves.
They need medical
attention immediately.
Tora! Can you hear me?
Tora!
It's a trap,
you have get out of here.
A trap?
It was her,
behind you.
[evil laughter]
Yaaaaah!
You know, it's a good thing
you guys are so quick,
because if you'd been
a split-second slower,
my Blaze would have
chopped you right in half!
Why are you doing this?
I don't get it!
You haven't figured it out yet?
I attacked you
because I'm the one
who took out these
two cretins here.
No way.
Tor, do you have any injuries?
You should check.
Right. [grunts]
You cut me.
How's this possible?
[chuckles]
You know what doesn't
make any sense to me?
These weapons could
smash through a brick wall
and yet, they don't seem
to do any harm to humans.
Blaze power is just the physical
manifestation of one's soul,
and, as we all know,
one's mental attitude can
shift in a variety of ways!
Your reactions are
truly impressive.
So you're saying if you wield
a Blaze with deadly intent,
that it can actually be used
to injure your opponent?
Looks like you're finally
starting to catch on,
Silverlocks!
[grunting]
Lesson one! 'Kay?
You can in fact use your Blaze
to hurt or even kill someone.
But this information
is super classified,
so you're gonna have
to keep it to yourselves!
And now for tonight's
second lesson.
We'll find out what happens when
someone's Blaze is destroyed!
[groaning]
[screaming]
Tora!
As you can see here,
His psyche takes enough damage
to keep him knocked out
for at least a day.
But if you stop
and think about it,
things could be
a whole lot worse
considering his spirit has been
pretty much annihilated.
You monster.
Why would you do that to him?
This is all in a day's work.
I guess you could think of it
as my own special way of
dealing with some of our
most promising newcomers.
Enough talk. I say we get
back to the business at hand.
[laughs]
It's time for you to die.
Above us! Tor!
[grunting]
[RITO shouting]
[whimpers]
Too slow!
[yelps]
Too bad, so sad!
Come on, put your back into it
since you're fighting
for your life and all!
[groans]
Pathetic.
This was even easier than
I thought it was going to be!
[screams]
Looks like it's
game over for you!
Julie.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Do you think now is
really the time
to worry about anyone
but yourself?
[groaning]
You're trying your best,
but it's not good enough.
You're going to die
because you're weak!
She only died
because she was too weak.
[growling]
Shut up!
Yah!
[gasps]
Oh, goodness!
If only that had
connected, am I right?
It's the time between attacks
that's really killing you!
[laughs maniacally]
[growls]
[TOR groans]
Are you okay, Tor?
[TOR grunts]
But she's definitely a
whole lot stronger than me.
And she's also a whole
lot faster than me.
All we need is one opportunity.
We could take her down if we
just landed a single solid hit.
I don't think there's any way
we're gonna get that lucky.
What, Tor?
So!
Have you decided which
one of you will die first?
Nej. I'll protect Tor
no matter what!
Ha! You two make
such an adorable young Duo.
It's hard-working students like
you who make your teacher proud!
Tor!
If you want to get to her,
you're gonna have
to go through me!
Ha! Fine with me,
you irregular freak!
If you want to be the first
to die, then so be it!
[grunting]
Take that!
And that! And that!
You can't do this alone!
Stay back!
I can handle this!
Let me help!
Guess what? You can swing
that sword of yours all day,
but it's never going
to dent my shield!
Bluffing isn't going to do
you any good here!
You were tenacious,
I gotta give you that,
but I'm afraid this is where
you bid your life farewell.
If you've got
any witty last words,
then now is the time
to say them.
[laughs maniacally]
All right.
I think there's only
one thing left to say and...
It's Julie, I...
[laughs]
Hang on!
You're confessing
your love for her now?
You guys are a barrel of laughs.
But the real fun will be
cutting you into ribbons!
Hiyaaah!
What?
Okay, Tor, take two!
[yelling]
You're still far too slow!
My Blaze? You can't!
Thanks for
all the lessons, Professor!
Now it's time to smash it.
Mjolnir!
[RITO screaming]
Let's toast to our
Novgladius victory.
Yeah.
Ow, ow, ow.
Julie,
you did a heck of a job jumping
in for that last combination.
Thanks to you,
I could focus long enough
to make that attack count.
I really appreciate it.
We did practice the "I, two"
combo over and over again.
Thing is,
Only you would realize
in all that craziness
that you had the power to
destroy Miss Tsukimi's Blaze.
Well. With Tora
and Tatsu both safe,
and Tsukimi apprehended,
I think we're all right for now.
Except.
Why would she say that
it's "all in a day's work"?
What do you think
she meant by that?
Mm.
Not that you'd know
anything about it.
The best thing
we can do right now
is focus on tending
to your wounds.
Yeah. Right.
[groans]
How about I help
you out a little?
[BOTH grunting]
Oh no, I'm so sorry, Tor.
We brought some
food for you guys.
Hungry?
Are you feeling
any better today, Tor?
Uh...
What? No, not again!
Tor, you lousy, no-good dog!
This isn't what it
looks like, I swear!
Deep down inside
I knew it all along!
Knew what all along?
Tell them
what happened, Julie!
Hmm?
[flames roaring]
[gasps]
What happened?
She only died
because she was too weak.
[screaming]
[gasps]
What's wrong, Tor?
I'm so sorry.
I was just having
a bad dream, that's all.
I'm going to go outside
and get some fresh air.
Why don't you go
back to sleep, okay?
Mm.
[JULIE]
Who's Otoha?
You kept repeating,
"Otoha, why?"
So, Tor.
Who is that?
Tell me.
Don't worry about it.
No, tell me.
I want to know.
Forget about it, okay?
I won't forgive you
if you don't, Tor.
I said drop it!
Is that the real reason
you're doing all of this?
Is that why you
took the Lukifer?
And the Blaze?
Julie?
What are you doing?
[gasps]
Don't you see that
I'm just like you?
I'm an Avenger.
[MIYABI]
Hey, Julie.
Have you heard about the new
transfer student from England?
[JULIE]
Nej. Nej, sorry. No time.
[MIYABI]
Is something wrong?
[JULIE] Tomorrow I'm
going shopping with Tor.
[MIYABI gasps]
[JULIE]
Next time: "Exception."
[MIYABI]
That sounds like a date to me!