[birds chirping]
[moans]
Is it morning already?
Huh?
[screams]
Wait, what is Julie
doing up here?
[grunts]
This is my bed, right?
Uh...
Um, Julie.
Listen.
Did you--
Sleep well?
Ja. Good morning.
Oh. Morning.
No, wait! Did you
sleep up here last night?
[FEMALE STUDENT]
Hey, isn't that--
[MALE STUDENT] That's them,
and I heard he's an Irregular.
[FEMALE STUDENT] I didn't know
coed Duos were even allowed.
Man, the rumors
are already flying.
[JULIE]
Is something wrong, Tor?
Huh? No. It's fine.
Hey, why don't we
sit right here?
Ja.
Please bless this food.
[WOMAN]
Good morning, Tor.
Hmm?
Yes. Morning.
Do you guys mind
if we join you?
Oh no, go right ahead.
Um, your names are
Tomoe and Miyabi, right?
Mhmm. That's us
and thanks so much.
Whoa, what are you eating,
the carnivore's delight
breakfast or something?
I guess I just
really like meat.
[sighs]
That's not too healthy.
A meal should be
balanced with items from
each food group, you know.
[TOR chuckles]
[giggles awkwardly]
Sorry 'bout her. I guess you
could say that Miyabi's still
a little awkward around guys.
Oh, yeah?
[whimpering]
[TOR thinking]
Like Julie was yesterday.
[TOMOE]
Let's get down to brass tacks.
The reason we chose to sit
here today should be obvious.
We are quite concerned
about the two of you.
Concerned?
Well, rules notwithstanding.
You're a guy and girl.
Both living in the same room.
Tell me. Isn't that awkward?
I mean, aren't you guys
a little weirded-out about it?
Nej. Tor is a
wonderful roommate.
Oh. How so?
He not only
carried me to bed,
but he also slept
with me last night.
[BOTH whimper awkwardly]
No, wait, listen, you're
taking it the wrong way.
This is just a big
misunderstanding, I swear!
I thought you
were a nice guy!
But you're a perv!
And a dog!
[RITO] It's said that
one person in a thousand
is suited for a Lukifer.
Now those people who've
been given Lukifers
not only get physically
stronger, class,
but mentally as well,
as the spirit-like entity
inside them gains power!
There's a name for that
soul-power once it takes shape,
so what is it,
you with the glasses?
Torasaki! And to
answer your question,
the embodiment of soul-power
is known as a Blaze, ma'am.
Bingo!
Next question,
what is the proper term
for those chosen people
suited for Lukifers
who can use a Blaze, class?
Mmmm, you,
with the boobs!
Um. Those people
are called Exceeds.
Bingo once again!
As for Blazes, they're
normally traditional
weapons of simple construction.
They can be swords or spears,
and in the case of Irregulars,
even stranger things, right?
You, the cohabitator!
We're not "cohabitators,"
we're roommates.
[STUDENTS laugh]
Huh?
[laughs awkwardly]
[STUDENTS whispering]
[growling]
All right, let's move on, class!
[sighs]
So yesterday it was you
and today it's Tomoe, huh?
I don't understand
why she's so upset.
It's because of what
you said this morning.
Y'know, about us
"sleeping together."
Hmm?
In our language...
it can also mean
something else.
[whispering]
Uh, I'll clarify what
really happened for her.
Please do.
Aside from that, you speak
our language really well.
Thank you.
My mama is an interpreter.
She taught me.
Oh. That's really neat.
Hmm?
But not the written
language, I see.
Nej, I'm still trying
to get the hang of it.
And since the Lukifer's
physical enhancement
serves as a multiplier, who
can tell me what that means?
You, Muscles!
[grunts]
Right!
The more you train your body,
the stronger you'll get--
exactly like he just said!
[grunts]
[STUDENTS]
What? How'd she understand that?
So therefore,
our curriculum
includes lots and lots
of battle training you'll
need to get stronger.
By the time it's done,
all of you will be muy macho!
[STUDENTS]
But we don't want to be macho!
Now class,
listen up, because Lukifers
have levels you can raise
in the Rite of Sublimation.
It's always held
at the end of term
and it requires
everything you've got.
Without training
both body and mind,
your Lukifer levels
will never rise!
Plus, if you don't raise them
by a single level all year,
then I'm afraid
you'll be expelled.
[STUDENTS]
Expelled?
You don't want that to happen,
which is why the next
thing we're diving into
is battle training!
Hooray! [giggles]
[drum roll]
[TOMOE] I bow down
and beg your forgiveness!
Wait, where did that come from?
I jumped to conclusions this
morning in the dining hall
but Julie explained everything
to me and I'm sorry.
I'm glad we got that cleared up,
but would you please
stop bowing down
in front of me like this?
But I feel this is the only
way I can make things right!
Come on,
knock it off, please!
It'll keep hanging
over me though!
Um...
Look, you already apologized
so you don't have to
do anything else, okay?
People are already
getting the wrong idea.
[gasps]
That guy's got game.
Ew, in the gym?
Oh, Tor!
I'm sorry for that, too!
I'll keep bowing down
till you forgive me!
No, stop, you're making
things even worse!
Oh. Yeah, you're right.
Sorry!
[BOTH scream]
[TOR grunts]
[muffled] Mmm, sorry!
Why do I have
to be such a klutz?
No, stop, be gentle, that's
a real sensitive area!
[gasps, screams]
[grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
I, I didn't do that on purpose!
I know! Just do something
and do it fast, okay?
Uh...
[claps]
That's a special pinning
technique, right?
[TOR and TOMOE]
No!
[STUDENTS grunting]
I wonder if Tomoe's had
any martial arts training.
She's good.
Ever heard of the
Tachibana School?
It was founded by her family
and you can see its influence
everywhere in martial arts.
It's legendary.
Oh, wow, really?
Y'know, I'm more impressed
with your roommate
since she's holding her own
against Tomoe like a real champ.
So what's the deal with
this chick anyway, Tor?
Well, to be honest,
I haven't really asked her.
What, why not?
Because we're only roommates and
in a temporary Duo for a week.
For my permanent Duo, I
want to partner with you, Tora.
You do? Okay, but what
if I don't want to?
Hey, c'mon,
a coed Duo is bad news.
Huh. Guess it was inevitable.
Okay, sure, as long as you can
prove you're not a weakling.
Oh, that won't be a problem.
Let's do this!
All right, let's see if
you've gotten any
stronger over
the last two years.
Come on!
[panting]
[TOMOE]
Thank you very much.
[JULIE]
Thanks to you as well.
It was nice being able to go
all-out like that for once.
I had fun.
Thank you.
Ja and likewise.
[MIYABI]
Um, Tomoe. Julie.
Oh great, thanks a bunch.
That's very kind,
Miyabi. Thanks.
You two are just incredible!
I couldn't believe my eyes!
Miyabi,
will you be my next
sparring partner?
[inhales sharply]
Who, me?
No, no, no!
I'm terrible so I wouldn't be
a good match for you at all.
All right then.
Well, training isn't just about
getting in the ring, you know.
Studying how other
people fight can be
another form of practice, too.
Huh?
[TOR and TORA grunting]
Wow, those two
have some real skill.
Yeah!
I think I could study
them for a long time!
[BOTH grunting]
[laughs]
[wind blowing]
[water running]
[soft piano]
[door opening]
Hmm?
Thank you for
waiting up for me, Tor.
Sure thing.
You didn't have to wait
outside, though, you know.
[TOR]
Actually, I kinda did.
So I guess you've
had training, huh?
Training in what?
Martial arts based on
what I saw today.
Oh, nej. Self-taught.
Self-taught and
you're that powerful?
Holy cow.
How did you and Tora
get so strong?
Well, we both attended a dojo
together when we were kids.
You had fun today.
That's because whenever
I'm sparring with Tora,
I can really let loose.
[laughs]
Oh, I see.
[upbeat music]
[TORA]
Waiting for her again, eh?
Hmm?
Yeah.
I just don't like her
to walk alone.
Are you her roommate
or her babysitter?
What's that supposed to mean?
Heh. Just what it sounds like.
[TOR]
Oh, Tora?
Yeah, what?
Our application, man.
We get to file it tomorrow.
Hmm?
[sighs]
Yeah, I'll be there.
Hey, Julie?
Huh?
Good job.
You made it through the first
week and it was a tough one.
Congrats.
Ja, and congratulations
to you, too.
So, um,
who did you ask to pair up
with for your official Duo?
Oh, that.
Well, I'm actually thinking
about asking Tomoe.
Fantastic choice.
You guys are pretty closely
matched in terms of power.
I bet you two'll make
one tough Duo.
Are you pairing with Tora?
Yeah.
Ah.
[soft piano]
[TOR] You like
cherry blossoms, don't you?
My Mama, she said,
this country has
the prettiest ones.
Oh, yeah?
So what's the verdict?
They're incredibly
gorgeous, Tor.
This is the second time for us
to be right here in this spot.
Huh?
The first day of school.
You were looking
at them just like I was.
Mm.
So you noticed me then, huh?
Ja.
I'm real glad I could see
them again with you.
It's so nice.
Yeah. Sure is.
Maybe next year we can
meet here again like this.
Mm.
Yes, maybe.
[bells jingling]
Ugh.
Huh?
[breathing softly]
Oh, come on!
Uh.
Huh?
[sleepily] Papa...
Aw, the poor thing must
really miss her family.
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST]
Students filing Duo applications
please form an orderly line!
You know the final deadline
isn't until six this evening.
So please settle down,
there's no need to rush!
[FEMALE STUDENT]
Actually, there is.
[MALE STUDENT]
Yeah, class is about to start!
[FEMALE STUDENT 2] Can't you
please make this go any faster?
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST]
Okay...
[TORA] Maybe we should
just come back later.
[TOR]
Yeah. I agree.
Oh, cool.
She said Tomoe
might be the one.
[TORA]
So tell me.
Who's the lucky partner your
roommate is pairing up with?
Looks like Julie's decided
to go with Tomoe.
[TORA] Hmm. I wouldn't mind
seeing those two go at it.
[GIRLS giggling]
OMG, that was so embarrassing!
I know!
I wonder why Professor
Bunbun never told us
we'd have to do that.
Tell me about it--
my heart is still pounding!
--What the--?
--What that was about?
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST]
Applying for a Duo?
I'll need your student IDs,
please.
Okay, since these are in order,
I'll just need you two
to pledge your Duo-hood.
Hold on, pledge?
Our Duo-hood?
You put one Blaze
over the other.
And then to make
your Duo official,
all you have to do is recite
this pledge and it will be.
Well, go ahead.
Do we have to read this stuff?
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST]
Yup, that's the rule.
You're taking
the plunge, too, huh?
Hi, Tomoe.
Miyabi.
Why are you two here?
[TOMOE] Just turning in our
application like you guys.
Right?
Yes. Even though
I'm still a little worried
that my lack of ability
might hold you back.
Well, you shouldn't be
and it won't!
Out of all the students
here at Koryo Academy,
only one could be
my Duo partner.
And I know without a doubt
that person is definitely you.
Wait, hold on just a second!
I thought... you were
teaming up with Julie.
Well, she did ask me
about becoming a Duo.
But by that time, I already
decided on Miyabi.
I'm afraid I had to
turn her down.
What?
Then Julie...
Um, guys?
If your Duo's to be official,
you have to say the pledge.
Tora, I'm sorry!
I understand.
Now go!
[TOR]
One hour left.
[bells jingling]
Was that...?
[TOR]
Julie!
Tor.
What is it?
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Why are you here?
Mm.
Because I thought,
maybe I could see
Gimle from this spot.
Well, can you?
[TOR]
I heard Tomoe turned you down.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because talking about it
wouldn't change anything
for one reason,
and another was that I
didn't want to bother you.
But we're a Duo. You can
always be honest with me.
Look, temporary or not,
we're still a Duo.
Partners are supposed
to rely on each other.
Julie.
Let's make
our Duo official.
[gasps]
But what about Tora?
Don't worry about him.
He understands.
And what if Tomoe gets
the wrong idea about us again?
You can straighten
things out with her again.
I don't have a grasp
of the written language.
I'll teach it to you then.
Um. Okay.
But if I say yes,
what happens if
I drink all of your apple tea?
I'll just buy some more,
it's not a big deal.
I want to protect you, Julie.
I want to be the one
you can rely on.
So please,
be a Duo with me.
[gasps]
You don't mind
pairing up with me?
Of course I don't.
I want to.
Ja.
[BOTH] We two shall remain
bound together always.
And do everything as a Duo
to the best of our ability.
In joy and sorrow.
In sickness and in health.
Until death do us part.
[TOR]
You're falling asleep.
You should get to bed.
Ja.
I didn't mean my bed.
Nej. A Duo is
always together.
That doesn't mean
they have to share a bed!
Nej. We swore it, Tor.
"To do everything as a Duo
to the best of our ability."
Look, we can't keep
sleeping in the same bed
because it's really weird!
But,
I sleep with my mama
every night back home.
That's sweet.
I'm like your mama?
No, wait, that's creepy!
Whoever you think I am,
I'm not your mama!
You are very special,
though, Tor.
Uh.
"Special" how?
Well, you feel kind of
like a papa to me.
Oh. Really?
Yes, so can I please
sleep up here with you?
Mm.
Sure, but only this once.
Ja.
[groans] It's gonna be
another long night.
What's that?
Ah, it's nothing.
Oh, well then. Good night.
And to you too, Tor.
Good night.
[RITO] So we'll hop and skip
and jump and prance,
and do the bunny dance!
La-la-la-la-la-la-
la-la-la-la-la-la!
[TOMOE]
Now that Duos are decided,
it's time for our first battle.
[MIYABI]
I hope we'll do okay!
[TOMOE] Don't worry.
No matter how strong they are,
no one can stand up
to the two of us, Miyabi!
[JULIE]
Next time, "Avenger."
[MIYABI] But I've got
a bad feeling about this.