Well, we managed to pull it off.
Ja. And it's all
thanks to you, Tor.
Exactly, that's my future
husband for you!
[chuckles] Yeah,
I guess he did alright.
[LILITH and TOR chuckle]
[K] Just where do you
think you're going?
[TOR growls]
This isn't over,
not by a long shot.
You bastard!
[grunting]
[Blaze shatters]
[screams]
A Blaze is your best weapon.
But it can also be
your greatest weakness.
[gunshot]
[yelps]
[gasps]
No, Lilith!
Tora!
Even an Exception like our
Miss Bristol here cracks easily.
Just as I thought.
Exceeds are no match at all.
Not against this
Destruction I now wield!
[grunts]
Julie!
[JULIE]
It's just a scratch!
[gasps]
[grunting]
You stopped it!
[laughs]
[grunting]
[groaning]
Do you think you can win
with her holding you back?
Of course I do!
She's my partner!
I don't understand this at all.
Needing another
person's presence
to make you stronger
is simply ridiculous.
Are you going to spout
some nonsense now
about your resolve and
how it's your strength?
[JULIE grunting]
Haaah!
[gasps]
No wonder you're both
so fragile and weak!
[TOR and JULIE grunting]
[JULIE yelps]
Now I'll show you
how powerless you really are!
Hey, pal, did you
forget about this?
Koryo Academy.
My, what a wonderful place.
[TOR gasps]
Here you learn together.
Compete together.
Laugh together.
Such an ideal spot to
spend your brightest years.
It's so wonderful, in fact,
it makes me sick!
No, stop it!
Agh!
[grunting]
Why the hell
are you doing this?
Is there nothing
you care about?
Nobody to keep safe?
Doesn't anything
matter to you?
Nothing does.
With the sole exception of
one very important thing.
Agh!
And that, Kokonoe,
is absolute power!
It means everything to me!
No, don't!
[STUDENTS screaming]
Not so fast, there!
You little turd!
[grunting]
[STUDENTS gasp]
Yaaaaah!
[exhausted sigh]
I've got things
taken care of here.
You smash that
prick to pieces, okay?
Absolutely, Miss Tsukimi!
Attaboy.
Guess I can forget about getting
a good night's sleep now.
Times like these make me think I
was nuts for becoming a teacher.
[STUDENTS gasp and whimper]
[STUDENTS laugh and cheer]
But,
the kids make it worthwhile.
What a futile gesture.
You don't really think that'll
help somehow, do you?
[JULIE] Nej. But it did
create a blind spot for us.
Eh?
[shouting]
That was clever.
[grunts]
From this close up,
I won't miss.
[TOR]
Are your injuries okay?
Ja, Tor.
They're only minor.
Brilliant move.
I won't let you get
another one, though.
[gasps]
Julie, look out!
Behind you!
[gasps]
Tor! No!
You see there?
I guess you really did
protect her, didn't you?
[TOR groaning]
[K] Now die a painful death
in front of your friend.
Just think.
It'll eat away at her soul every
day for the rest of her life.
No, Tor.
Don't die.
Please, Tor.
No.
Please, Tor!
Don't die!
Your precious little
partner's calling for you!
Can't you hear her whine?
Stand up!
--[JULIE] Tor?
--[K] Take out your Blaze!
Tor!
You said you'd
always protect her.
C'mon, Kokonoe!
[K laughs]
[JULIE] You won't get
away with this.
Never.
Never, ever.
You'll never
get away with this!
Ah, there it is.
Yes, that overwhelming
dark power
that you once
wounded me with.
[screaming]
[screams]
[JULIE grunting]
[JULIE grunting and screaming]
[screams]
Her power.
It's incredible!
She may be even stronger
than this Destruction!
She can't be!
I have to be the
strongest one, me!
This is the end for you!
Hyaaaaaaaaah!
[screaming]
[groans]
[sparks buzzing]
[groaning]
I have to help Julie.
[JULIE screaming]
No, you can't.
Don't do this.
Please stop.
[groaning]
[TOR]
Julie!
Stop this!
Kokonoe.
You live.
It's no use.
I've gotta Blaze!
Aegis Desire!
Hyah!
[screaming]
[TOR]
Julie.
Look, I know where
you're coming from.
Someone very dear
to you was killed.
So you've been seeking
power to avenge them.
[JULIE screams frantically]
[TOR]
You're an Avenger.
Just like me, remember?
But there's
something that I've
been struggling
with for a while.
Do I want power?
Or do I want revenge?
There's a fine line
between them, so.
How is my power any
different from his?
[screaming]
But Julie,
thanks to you I now know.
[bells jingling]
[TOR]
The time we've spent together.
It's made me
realize something.
All that I want to do
is protect people.
That's why my soul power,
my Blaze--
it isn't a weapon,
but a shield.
Since I want to protect.
That's what my
power is meant for!
[screaming]
[TOR]
And that's why, Julie.
I'm going to protect you, too!
[groaning]
[screams]
Julie. That's enough.
I'm not dead, see?
I'm alive and right here.
[screaming]
So please.
Come back to me, Julie!
I'm here, Tor.
I'm glad to have
you back, Julie.
Tor, I could've killed you but
you risked your life.
Like I've told you before
I will always protect you.
Your big brother will always
protect you, okay, Kev?
The strength of your resolve.
There is no such thing!
[growling]
Just give it up.
Continuing's pointless.
You're right.
But everything's
pointless once you've lost.
And that's why I'm going
to kill the both of you!
Because this power
is the only thing
I have left!
Fine, then I will
protect her to the end!
Julie?
No, we'll protect each other.
Because you and I
are Duo partners, Tor.
That's right.
[BOTH]
Now, Aegis Desire!
Time for you to die,
Tor Kokonoe!
Julie Sigtuna!
I've done it!
What? How?
What I give Julie...
And what I give to Tor...
[BOTH]
Is protection!
That's impossible!
Where did
this power come from?
[TOR]
That's simple.
Alone, I couldn't defeat you.
But,
by my side I have Julie.
We're friends and partners
bound to each other!
That's what makes us a Duo.
That doesn't matter to me!
I will never lose
to the likes of you!
[yelps]
Julie!
My Blaze, Tor.
Please take it,
and use it with yours!
Gotcha!
[panting]
Yaaaaah!
Hiyaaaaaaaaah!
Ahhhhh!
[BOTH screaming]
[K]
Ryan.
[panting]
[grunts]
[laughs weakly]
[bells jingling]
[birds chirping]
[MIYABI]
I'm sorry!
Uh?
I brought this on you guys.
This is all my fault,
and I'm so sorry!
Uh.
[TOR]
Look.
Why don't we forget it and all
work on getting stronger?
Yeah, we will!
And you know why?
Because you're my partner!
And likewise I've got
you as mine, Tomoe!
Miyabi, Tomoe, Tora, Tatsu.
We can do this together!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[RITO] Would you damn pests quit
following me around already?
[STUDENTS]
Wait up!
Dark Professor Bunbun, please!
[RITO] Leave me alone
or I'll have you brats
--running laps for days!
--Whoa, what's up with them?
Tsukimi defended the dorms
so now she's their hero.
[TATSU grunts]
Oh.
Okay.
[birds chirping]
[LILITH]
Here you go.
It's a gift for you, Tor.
Thanks, but what is it?
[LILITH] Materials
on Kevin Wayfair.
He was the young man
who we knew only as "K."
[gasps]
It turns out, he once
had an older brother.
One he was very close to
but also lost quite suddenly.
K's family then fell apart,
and as for himself, he
wound up in the shadows,
sold off into that
old man's organization.
He not only lost his brother,
but also his family
and his name.
Smith raised him
as a soldier who
sought only power and results.
That's the long and short of K.
[TOR]
So why would you give me this?
[LILITH] Well, I thought you
might be a little bit curious.
Thanks for thinking
of me, Lilith.
Don't mention it.
You are my future husband.
[TOR chuckles]
Oh, and about the other thing
that's been concerning you.
Huh?
I heard she left
the hospital today.
I've gotta go!
[sighs]
To be honest, Tor.
I can't say I like that
reaction of yours.
[gasps]
[exhales]
Mm.
However, I know you haven't
seen her all this time.
So I suppose I'll
allow it for today.
Off you go!
Spit spot!
Again, Lilith.
Thank you!
You're being incredibly
kind to Tor, you know,
by letting him see
the file on K like that.
Tor's soul has developed,
and I'd like to see
it do so even further.
And learning why his enemy felt
what he did might fuel that.
Sakuya. You haven't changed.
That's right.
It's so the path
that I'm on now
will one day reach
Absolute Duo, you see.
So, that's why.
[panting]
[uplifting music]
[bells jingling]
[TOR] Well, can you see
Gimle from here?
[JULIE]
Nej. Unfortunately.
Hey, Tor.
I want to confess that
I'm not an Exceed.
Huh?
The day that Papa was killed.
I did more than just
pray to get stronger.
I begged for it.
And then...
I found myself with fangs.
For the sake of revenge.
By wanting to get stronger I had
awakened the power within me.
So I'm not an Exceed.
What I am is an El Awake.
And what exactly
is an El Awake?
[JULIE] They're certain people
who have power hidden inside.
It's tucked away in
the depths of their souls.
Eventually their
power awakens and
it makes
weapons of their souls.
They are called El Awakes.
[TOR]
Wait a minute.
How is that any
different than an Exceed?
Well, actually, I've heard
that Exceeds are El Awakes,
but the difference
is they've had their
soul-powers
artificially awakened.
I couldn't control the power
when it emerged, it was awful.
But luckily, the Dorn Agency
stepped in and rescued me.
[TOR]
So that's what happened?
[JULIE] I'm sorry I never
told you about this, Tor.
I've been so afraid.
Afraid you'd find out
I wasn't an Exceed.
Afraid that once
you knew everything
about me and what I was,
that you'd drift away and then
I'd never get to see you again.
But more than anything,
I've been afraid that my
power would hurt you,
or worse, possibly
even kill you.
[TOR]
Julie.
[JULIE]
Even so,
Tor, I still--
I want be with you!
And be your Duo partner!
I can't help it!
I'm sorry!
[cries]
I need to apologize
to you as well.
Huh?
After I first saw your true
power back on K's boat,
I told myself,
"I can't let her use
that thing again."
Using it hurt you bad,
so doing it again
was out of the question.
But I went and let
you do just that.
And by doing so, it's my fault
you got hurt once more.
[JULIE]
No, it's not!
[TOR]
It's all right.
Just watch.
I'm gonna get stronger.
Strong enough to really protect
you when you need it. I promise.
Listen to me, Julie.
I want you
to keep being my Duo.
[TOR and JULIE]
Blaze on!
[BOTH] We two shall
remain together always,
and do everything as a Duo,
to the best of our ability.
In joy and sorrow.
In sickness and in health,
until death do us part.
We are a Duo,
now and forever.