You see?
It's me.
But as you can tell,
I've been reborn.
[gasps]
No.
What have those monsters
done to you, Miyabi?
You look just like--
[ETHNARCH]
Stand back, guys!
Let's take her down, team!
[ETHNARCH TEAM]
Right!
No, don't!
She's our friend!
Blaze on.
[ALL screaming]
You're in my way.
[gasps]
[growls]
[MIYABI giggles]
Did you see how easy
that was for me?
Well, Tor?
I want you to see how
strong I am now.
Miyabi.
What have they done to you?
[laughing]
We just gave her a gift.
That's all.
A heavens-piercing,
god-slaying gift.
Hey, Tor. Get ready.
[MIYABI]
[shocked grunts]
Watch out!
Thank you. That was close.
There's no need to thank me.
I'm just glad that you're okay.
[TOR grunts]
It looks like
you're interfering.
I am. And I'll keep
doing so, too.
I'll stop anyone from
hurting Tor, even you.
Blaze on!
[STUDENTS]
She's got the power to lay out
a bunch of Ethnarchs.
That's way stronger than
a Level 2 like her should be.
There are ways to enhance
one's strength quickly.
That must be the case.
You mean Miyabi's been
enhanced with Rebel technology?
Precisely!
What you see before you
is the crowning achievement
of Equipment Smith's
research and development.
She's the perfect combination
of Exceed and Unit!
[MASTER ARMORER] What do you
think now, Miss Witch?
The power that you tried
so hard to keep from me
is really quite incredible,
wouldn't you say?
Now feast your eyes upon
my greatest masterpiece!
It's only a matter of time until
she wins and makes me
the victor
of this killing game!
A Fusion,
of an Exceed and a Unit?
Correct.
And it was completed with her
full cooperation, of course.
This bold young woman
made stopping by your
wretched little island
worth the effort.
[growls]
How dare you!
You get your hands off of her!
Filthy swine!
[laughs]
Miyabi!
He somehow forced you
into doing this, didn't he?
Don't you worry!
We're gonna protect you, okay?
Protect me?
Get away from her, Tomoe!
Huh?
[TOR]
Tomoe!
No.
I don't think I require your
protection any longer.
You're so weak.
Especially compared to me.
[groans]
Miyabi.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, that's right!
A Blaze can harm
flesh and blood.
When it's wielded
with deadly intent.
Oh, no.
Miyabi's probably
been brainwashed.
[gasps]
Or something very similar
to that, I'd wager.
[SAKUYA]
I can only assume
that you've been
keeping a close eye
on this Academy's students
for quite some time now.
[MASTER ARMORER] The battle-
hardened body of an Exceed
combined with such a
delicate and imbalanced spirit.
Once you factor in
how desperately
she yearns for strength,
that young woman was
truly the ideal candidate.
With just the slightest
bit of encouragement,
she has harnessed a power
beyond our wildest dreams.
And grown to become
the perfect soldier.
One who'll fight to
the death, if ordered.
Perhaps you've had
a change of heart.
About the alliance
that we talked about?
Well, then?
[SAKUYA]
Yes.
I've made a decision.
Oh?
First we have to get rid
of your inside men.
We can't have a pitiful
old man spying on
female students for
some clandestine purpose,
which I'm sure wasn't
just for research, either.
[laughs]
When you put it that way,
it does sound pretty creepy!
[laughs loudly]
[growls]
That man gave me
this incredible power.
I was so weak.
And now look at
how strong I've become.
Brainwashing is despicable!
I won't argue with you there.
But she asked
for this herself.
We didn't need
to brainwash her.
Ridiculous!
There's no way Miyabi would
ask for this kind of power!
[laughs]
Do you honestly believe I don't
want strength like this?
You really are very funny.
You are.
But,
you know nothing about me
or what I want, Tomoe.
[gasps]
Don't say that.
[K] A young woman
on a quest for power
all for the love of a boy
who rejected her.
[K laughs]
It's quite heroic,
don't you think?
Maybe now you
realize you've been
under observation
all this time.
[TOR]
Stop it.
I must admit it was amusing.
It almost felt like
I was watching some
preposterous teen movie.
Shut up!
Blaze on!
Miyabi?
Tell me why you've always
looked at everyone except me.
Tell me.
Why, Tor?
How is she so strong?
Look at me! Look!
Look at me, Tor!
Look how strong I am now!
Miyabi! [grunts]
See? Look, Tor!
Don't just stand there,
you blockhead!
We must deal with Miyabi.
Are you going to help?
Ja.
If we only use Blazes,
I think we can stop her
without actually hurting her.
You guys.
[MIYABI]
Interrupting me again?
Why don't you understand?
That all I need is Tor!
Julie!
Don't worry. I'm fine!
[MIYABI] Did you see how
easy that was for me?
Well, Tor? I want you to see
how strong I am now.
Miyabi.
[MIYABI]
Remember?
When it was just
the two of us on the beach?
And then you told me
you were too weak.
That's why.
I decided then and there
I was going to get stronger.
That I wouldn't let
anything hurt you.
That's the only reason
I'm doing all of this.
I thought that if I could
protect you from everything,
maybe you'd love me.
And then, we could
be together, forever.
But teaming up with
these Rebels is insane!
-[grunting]
-[metal clanging]
Oh Tor, Tor, Tor,
oh Tor, Tor, Tor, Tor!
Miyabi.
[TOMOE thinking]
I, I had no idea.
[slow clapping]
Bravo
Not only did you prove yourself
most effective
against Exceeds,
you took on an Exception.
Impressive.
But unfortunately for me,
playtime is just about over.
And where do you
think you're going, K?
[K laughs]
I know that we're in the middle
of our little game and all--
[gunshots and shouting]
But I have other
matters to attend to.
I'm afraid I must
greet the Blaze Diabolica
on behalf of the corps.
[LILITH gasps]
You wouldn't dare hurt Sakuya!
[K] With her intelligence
and resourcefulness,
I'm certain that the witch will
make an excellent test subject.
I bid you adieu.
I sincerely hope
that all involved
enjoy the rest of the game.
[growls] Not so fast!
Look out!
No, look at my power.
Soon I'll have more.
And more! And more!
And more!
And more and more!
Just stay
and watch me, Tor.
Huh?
Tomoe!
[grunts]
Hey, guys? Listen.
I'm gonna need you to let me
deal with Miyabi by myself.
But that's insane!
Yeah, I know what
it sounds like.
It's just--
If there's
a way to help my Duo.
I have to try!
[TOMOE]
Go.
I can take care of this!
Come on. Let me go!
That's enough.
We should leave them.
Let's go.
[TOR]
But Julie--
Listen.
We should trust her,
and the bonds shared by a Duo.
All right.
[TORA]
No objection here.
She's all yours, Tomoe.
[MIYABI]
And now, he's gone.
Interrupted yet again.
I won't let you get
away with this, Tomoe.
Miyabi.
You should know I'll be
the one to stop you.
[TOR]
Rebels.
[BOTH grunt]
Lilith! Tora!
--[gunshots]
--[slashing and screaming]
We'll hold them off
here as long as we can!
I usually won't
say things again.
But this time,
I'll gladly do so.
Please go help Sakuya!
We're on it!
Ja!
[slashing and screaming]
Hmph.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you
got the short end of the stick.
Everyone knows a wife's
duty is to stand by her man.
No matter how bad things get.
You're way more of a weirdo
than I thought,
Miss Lilith Bristol.
So are you, Aoi Torasaki.
[TORA] Okay, shall we do
this as an ad-hoc Duo?
[LILITH] Yep! We two shall
remain together always,
and so on and so forth.
C'mon!
Go big or go home!
[TOR]
K?
What took you two so long?
You're not after
the Headmistress?
I knew you'd come running if I
threatened your precious Sakuya.
Honestly,
I only want one thing.
And that's revenge for
our last encounter.
More than anything,
Tor Kononoe,
I want to see the look
of despair on your face
when the person you
swore to protect is dead!
And gone!
I can tell you right now
that your wishes
won't be coming true.
We're not about
to let that happen!
Do you hear me?
Ugh!
How long will you keep
getting in my way?
[TOMOE]
For as long as it takes!
That's right!
And I'll keep doing it
till you give up that
crazy borrowed power,
you hear me?
I don't understand
what your problem is.
Our Lukifers are basically
just borrowed power, too.
You're wrong!
Our Lukifers won't work
if we're not always
trying to better ourselves!
What we gain from dedication,
hard work and
overcoming difficulty.
That's real strength!
Isn't that the reason why you
worked so hard for so long?
It was...
for him.
What do you mean?
It was for him!
[groans]
You're wrong!
I didn't train every day to
better myself, Tomoe!
It was for Tor!
I wanted the person
I liked to notice me!
That's all!
[gasps]
A young woman on
a quest for power all for
the love of a boy
who rejected her.
It's heroic.
[TOMOE]
I see.
I really don't know anything.
--[grunting]
--[metal clashing]
It seems to me you two
are being rather cold-hearted.
You left behind
one single friend
to try
and take on the Fusion?
That's not what
sane people do, is it?
Don't waste your time
trying to psych us out.
We believe in
the bond they share.
A Duo's bond.
Whatever's happening, we
know that they'll work it out.
I'd better hurry if I
want to catch up to Tor.
[TOMOE]
We're not done.
Please. Give it a rest.
[grunts]
You were right.
I really don't know
anything about you.
But still--
That power of yours is
wrong and you know it!
Tor would say the same thing.
[gasps]
[TOMOE] That's the kind of
honesty you can expect from him.
Don't say that!
All I wanted to do was
get stronger for him!
Tor would never try to
tear me down like that!
[gasps]
Then tell me one thing.
Miyabi,
did you tell him how,
well,
how you felt about him?
Yes, I did.
And then,
he rejected me.
Because I was so weak.
I see.
Well, in that case,
you don't need that
kind of power after all.
Don't you start on that again!
[TOMOE] But only because you're
so incredibly strong already!
[gasps]
I'm not good at girl stuff.
I don't know even
know how to flirt.
And I--
I've never once been in love.
But,
despite all that,
I still know how
hard it must be to
confess your
feelings to someone.
Miyabi.
Believe me,
you're strong.
So much stronger
than someone like me.
[gasps]
You think I'm stronger?
I'm ashamed to
have thought I was
supporting you all this time.
And that's why,
I can't bear to see you drowning
in all of that false power!
You were brave enough
to tell Tor how you felt,
so I know you can get
stronger without that stuff!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
If I don't have this power,
there's no way
I'll ever be able
to face Tor again!
And if I just hang
on to it, then I know
that he'll want to be
with me forever!
[TOMOE] Don't give up!
You've got to keep trying
with your true strength!
I'll never be good enough
for that to work!
I can't stand the thought
of being rejected again.
I'm so sick of all
the sadness and pain.
I can't take it.
[TOMOE]
You have me!
Anytime you're ever in pain.
You can count on me
to comfort you.
Let's both get
stronger together.
Okay?
Like a real Duo should!
That sounds...
so nice.
[screaming]
Concentrate on the sound
of my voice, Miyabi!
--Concentrate!
--Shut up!
I will destroy anything and
everything that gets in my way!
First I have to say,
I'm so sorry.
I wish that I was
more clever than I am.
But this is the only
way I can think of
to make you open your eyes.
So, brace yourself!
Miyabi.
Tomoe.
Are you okay, Miyabi?
You can slap.
That really hurt me.
Yeah.
It hurt me, too.
Tomoe.
I'm so sorry.
Don't mention it.
We are a Duo.
Yeah.
We sure are.
Thank you,
Tomoe.
What? No, how could
the device stop working?
That's impossible!
I don't understand!
[TOR]
Ha! We told you, K!
[JULIE]
We knew Tomoe could do it.
Miyabi is free now!
Don't celebrate just yet.
This isn't over!
[TOR]
Julie!
Ah, there it is!
[clapping]
I knew I'd get to see it!
It's priceless! The look
on your face when
the one you swore
to protect gets hurt!
And we're just getting started!
Now, why don't you show me
more of that pathetic face?
--[gunshots]
--[TOR grunting]
[TOR]
Julie.
You alright?
Ja. It's just a scrape.
[gasps]
Tor! You're bleeding!
[TOR]
Heh. It's no big deal.
[K clapping]
How magnificent!
Your resolve to protect your
friend is the real deal.
And, oh, so charming!
I did want a sound bite.
I was really hoping
for a tearful goodbye
as your beloved friend lie
dying in your arms, perhaps.
This is low.
Even for you.
You know people like you
make me physically ill.
Risking your life to
protect a special someone?
I can't think of anything
else more revolting.
Run, Tor!
Get out of here!
Don't worry about me!
Save yourself!
[TOR] Of course I'm going
to worry about you!
[JULIE]
Tor!
[TOR]
Hey, K. Listen.
I'll kill you!
I swear that I'll kill you!
I want to protect you, Julie.
I wanna be the one
you can rely on.
Julie, stop!
Still,
keep in mind the world
waits for no one,
nor is it so kind to
let you have your way.
To keep her safe from anything
that might threaten her,
I'll do whatever it takes.
And, yes,
that includes this!
And what good
will that do?
You'll see.
It'll affect the embodiment
of my soul-power, my Blaze!
So!
Hope you're ready, K!
Fire!
[TOR grunts]
[gunshots]
[K]
What?
But how?
This cannot be happening!
How can you still
be alive after that?
To protect her.
That's the reason
I'm still standing!
Kill him!
--[grunts]
--[thuds]
Huh?
[slashing]
[groans]
We made it just in time
for the last dance.
Heh. Let's make it
a quick one, shall we?
I'm going to go
finish this, okay?
Ja.
[bells jingling]
I'll be waiting for you.
K!
It all ends
with this one blow.
You're the one going
down, Kokonoe!
Head off the fang!
Aegis Desire!
It can't be!
Hyaaah!
Pierce and then crush!
Yaaaaaaaah!
He's down.
[TOR]
Hey.
We won!
[MASTER ARMORER]
Impossible!
[grunts]
How could my Units have
been defeated like this?
[SAKUYA] It appears
as though this evening's
soiree has come to an end.
What a farce this
turned out to be.
[laughing] Well, I thought it
was extremely entertaining!
Right.
See you at
the next conference.
Au revoir, everyone.
What do you think now?
Has this changed
your mind about what
you called "antiquated"
soul power?
If you still don't
understand it,
perhaps it's time to
admit that it's beyond you.
[giggles]
[grunts]
She's just a girl!
I can understand how I lost
to her grandfather years ago
but losing to a giggling child?
[SAKUYA]
Tor Kokonoe.
Will you live up to all
my expectations?
I hope so.
[K thinking]
I-- I lost?
To that weakling?
But how?
[grunts]
[MASTER ARMORER]
K, you pathetic worthless stray!
How dare you let
that brat of a girl
make a fool out
of me like that?
This is all your fault,
imbecile, do you hear me, yours!
[grunting]
[MASTER ARMORER] Have
you forgotten the generosity
and the kindness
that I showed to you?
Scum like you doesn't
even deserve to live!
[laughing]
Huh?
You actually find this funny?
I guess there's only one
course of action left to take.
[laughs]
Now go forth and
destroy everything!
Kill the girl
and burn down the school!
[groans]
You-- you bastard.
I see now
that the only person you
can trust is yourself.
[groans]
Help me.
No one can hear you.
No one will come to
protect you, old man.
Ugh!
Having a stingy old crank like
you around might ruin my plans.
And now,
this is mine.
I have the ultimate armor.
Destruction!
And I will use it
to destroy Kokonoe
and his friends!
[TOR]
I've always wondered.
Why does my soul-power
take the form of a shield?
Well now I finally
know the answer.
And it's because of you.
[JULIE] Next time,
the finale: "Absolute Duo."
[BOTH]
Head off the fang! Aegis Desire!