- ( chopper blades whir )
- ( brakes screech )
- Soldier: PROFESSOR,
PLEASE GET DOWN.
HIT THAT CHOPPER
WITH EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
- ( gunfire )
- ( grunting )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( gasps )
- CIA Operative:
AT 1800 HOURS LAST NIGHT,
IN THE CAUCASUS
REPUBLIC J,
A HIGHLY ARMED
PARA-MILITARY GROUP
OF UNKNOWN ORIGIN ELIMINATED
DR. ELENA BABURIN'S
GUARD DETACHMENT
AND ABDUCTED HER.
DR. BABURIN WAS
PREVIOUSLY CONFINED
TO A REPUBLIC J
RESEARCH FACILITY
AS THEY THEMSELVES
HAD ABDUCTED HER
THREE YEARS BEFORE.
SHE IS REGARDED AS
THE WORLD'S FOREMOST EXPERT
ON QUANTUM OPTICS.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Koko: WELL, GANG,
THINGS ARE GONNA BE
REALLY BUSY
FROM HERE ON OUT.
WE'RE GOING ON A
'ROUND-THE-WORLD BUSINESS TRIP.
- IS IT JUST ME, BOSS,
OR DOES JONAH LOOK
GRUMPIER THAN NORMAL?
YOU'D THINK HE'D LIKE HAVING
THAT BULLET OUT OF HIS BUTT.
- A LITTLE BIT OF PAIN NOW
HAS TO BEAT SETTING OFF
AIRPORT METAL DETECTORS
ALL THE TIME.
COME ON, JONAH, CHEER UP.
LET'S GO, GO, GO.
- ( machine whirs loudly )
- Man: EXCUSE ME, SIR.
SIR, YOU GOT A PHONE CALL!
- COOL, I GOT TO TAKE THIS.
- HIRO, IF YOU'RE
GOING INTO TOWN,
PICK ME UP SOME ICE CREAM.
- NO PROBLEM, DAD.
- Schokolade: UGH!
I FEEL LIKE I'M GONNA MELT.
WHAT THE HELL KIND
OF COUNTRY HAS SEPTEMBER
BE ITS HOTTEST MONTH?
ENDURING THIS KIND OF WEATHER
FOR INTEL
IS SO NOT WORTH IT.
"BUT KOKO'S BEEN ACTING STRANGE.
FOLLOW HER EVERY MOVE,
JUST DON'T GET YOUR
DUMB-ASS CAUGHT."
YEAH, THANKS A CRAP-TON,
SCARECROW.
THIS JOB AIN'T GONNA BE EASY.
KOKO AND HER UNIT
ALL KNOW WHAT I LOOK LIKE.
SO I CAN'T
EXACTLY SHADOW THEM.
BUT I GUESS I'LL DO
WHAT I GOTTA.
IT IS MY FORTE.
NEVER BEEN SPOTTED,
LET ALONE CAPTURED.
SO THEN WHY IS SCARECROW
ALWAYS RIDING MY BUTT?
YOU WON'T YELL AT ME,
WILL YOU FRIED OCTOPUS BALL?
YOU DO NOTHING BUT PROVIDE
CRUNCHY, JUICY DELICIOUSNESS!
SO WORTH IT!
I WANT MORE!
THANKS TO KOKO'S
GLOBE HOPPING.
I CAN SAMPLE EVERY
LOCAL DELICACY!
- Scarecrow: THAT DUMB BIMBO.
I'M SURE SHE'S WASTING TIME
EATING RIGHT NOW,
INSTEAD OF WORKING.
- Hacker: THIS WEAPONS CHICK
IS LOADED.
- HUH?
- MOST OF KOKO'S ASSETS
WERE IN STOCKS AND BONDS.
BUT TWO YEARS AGO, SHE STARTED
LIQUIDATING EVERYTHING
IN A VERY CONTROLLED,
DELIBERATE MANNER TOO--
CAREFUL NOT TO RUFFLE
THE GLOBAL MARKETS
OR AROUSE SUSPICION FROM
SECURITY AND
EXCHANGE COMMISSIONS.
STILL, WHILE FAINT,
SHE HAS LEFT A TRAIL.
HER ASSETS PASS THROUGH
SWISS DUMMY CORPORATIONS
BEFORE BEING INVESTED
IN MARCHEN.
AND OF COURSE
IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING
THEY USED THAT CAPITAL
TO BUILD THEIR SECOND FACTORY
IN SOUTH AFRICA.
- ANYTHING WITH THAT BANK
H.C.L.I. INVESTS IN?
HEKMA-IB?
- NO, NOT EVEN FOR
A SINGLE TRANSACTION.
- MEANS SHE'S KEEPING
THIS MARCHEN STUFF
SECRET FROM
THE HOME OFFICE.
YOU THINK KASPER AND FLOYD
HAVE CAUGHT ON?
- CAN'T FIND ANY SIGN.
MAYBE THEY'RE DIGGING
INTO HER RECORDS
ON THE SLY TOO.
( clicking )
I JUST DON'T GET WHY
AN ARMS DEALER
WOULD START SINKING ALL
HER MONEY INTO A TOY FACTORY,
UNLESS IT'S NOT ONE.
THE CASH FLOW
IS A LOT MORE IN LINE
WITH A MILITARY INSTALLATION.
MAYBE SHE WANTS
A VERTICAL MONOPOLY
TO MANUFACTURE WHAT
SHE DISTRIBUTES.
IT IS EVERY DEALER'S DREAM.
- EVERY VILLAIN'S DREAM.
CLOSER WE SEEM TO GET,
THE SNEAKER KOKO GETS.
IT'S LIKE SHE'S ALWAYS
FIVE STEPS AHEAD OF US.
BY THE TIME WE NAIL DOWN
HER PLANS, IT'LL BE TOO LATE.
IF I GOTTA, I'LL TEAM UP WITH
THE FAT MAN BACK AT LANGLEY.
SNIFFING OUT THE MONEY TRAIL
IS WHAT I DO.
AND I WILL CATCH UP TO HER.
YOU MESS WITH THE SCARECROW,
YOU'RE GONNA GET BURNED!
- Koko: NICE TO MEET YOU,
MR. KISARAGI.
- OH, THE PLEASURE'S ALL MINE,
MISS HEKMATYAR.
THANKS FOR MAKING THE TREK
OUT TO SEE ME IN THIS HEAT.
IT'S BEEN
UNSEASONABLY WARM
FOR JAPAN
- ( giggles )
IF I COULDN'T STAND
A LITTLE HEAT,
I WOULDN'T MAKE IT VERY FAR
IN THIS BUSINESS.
- Lutz: HEY, VALMET.
YOU NOTICED THE LITTLE LADY
GETTING MORE...
AGGRESSIVE LATELY?
- WHAT? YOU TALKING ABOUT
THE DR. BABURIN JOB?
YEAH, I HAD A FEELING
YOU'VE HAD SOMETHING
WEIGHING ON YOUR MIND.
DID YOU THINK WE'VE
BEEN MORAL CRUSADERS
ON THE SIDE OF JUSTICE
ALL THIS TIME?
THE MISSIONS ALONG
THE PATH KOKO WALKS
REQUIRE EACH OF US
TO TAKE MEASURES
SOME MIGHT CONSIDER DRASTIC.
OUR JOB IS TO SUPPORT KOKO,
NOT TO QUESTION HER.
( cracking )
IN FACT, LUTZ,
YOU GOT A WHOLE LOT OF NERVE
SECOND-GUESSING KOKO
IN MY PRESENCE!
YOU WANT TO SEE AGGRESSIVE?!
OH, YOU KNEW HOW I'D ANSWER
BEFORE YOU EVEN ASKED.
YOU JUST WANTED
YOUR GRIEVANCES ON THE TABLE.
MAYBE SHE HAS
GOTTEN AGGRESSIVE.
NOT SURE.
I'LL GIVE IT MORE THOUGHT.
BUT I BELIEVE IN KOKO.
- I'D LIKE KISARAGI
PHOTOCHEMICAL ENGINEERING
TO ISSUE 10 MILLION
NEW SHARES FOR ME TO PURCHASE.
THAT WAY,
I'LL BECOME BOTH
YOUR MAJORITY SHARE HOLDER
AND YOUR LARGEST INVESTOR.
- I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH,
MISS HEKMATYAR.
YOUR INVESTMENT MEANS
WE CAN CONTINUE OUR PROJECT
WITHOUT INTERRUPTION.
OF COURSE,
I'D BE LYING IF I SAID
SOME OF OUR MINOR INVESTORS
AND CREDITORS
WOULDN'T TAKE ISSUE WITH
YOUR MODEST POWER PLAY.
- TELL THEM THE STOCK
WOULDN'T IMPROVE
SO LONG AS
YOU WERE IN THE RED.
ACCEPT MY INVESTMENT.
CONTINUE YOUR PROJECT
AND REORGANIZE
THE BUSINESS-END OF THINGS.
DO THAT AND THE OTHER
SHARE HOLDERS WILL APPROVE.
IF NEED BE, I CAN PROVIDE
A PROFESSIONAL
RESTRUCTURING CONSULTANT.
I SEE THE VALUE
IN THE FUTURE
YOU AND YOUR FATHER
ARE TRYING TO CREATE.
I'D LIKE TO MAKE IT REAL.
QUANTUM DOT PHOTONIC
CRYSTAL NANODEVICES,
SPEND WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET THEM INTO PRODUCTION.
- DONE.
- AND I CAN TELL YOU
WHERE I WANT THEM DELIVERED.
- Hinoki: OSAKA, TAIPEI,
SHANGHAI, SINGAPORE,
AND NOW AMERICA?
KOKO AND HER TEAM
ARE KEEPING BUSY.
- AH, MISTER HINOKI,
BACK FROM THE BEACH.
LOOKING GOOD, I MUST SAY.
- THANKS.
NOT NEARLY AS GOOD AS YOU,
MISS HEKMATYAR.
I'M SORRY FOR SURPRISING YOU
AT THE AIRPORT LIKE THIS,
BUT WE NEED TO TALK.
- SURE, NO PROBLEM.
THERE'S A RESTAURANT HERE
WE CAN GO TO.
- Black: MISS HEKMATYAR.
YOU LIKE
BURGER JOINTS TOO, RIGHT?
I KNEW YOU'D PICK
THIS PLACE.
- EVERYONE, ORDER
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
LUNCH IS ON THE C.I.A.
- Guys: SWEET.
- Black: WHAT?!
OH SHIT.  AT AIRPORT PRICES,
THAT'S GONNA STING.
OH, WELL, HAVE A SEAT.
YOU TOO, COLONEL.
JONAH, ORDER ANYTHING
ON THE MENU.
THIS PLACE HAS TWO OF MY
ALL-TIME FAVORITE BURGERS.
- Koko: YOUR TABLE'S FILTHY.
ANY GOOD?
- HM-HMM.
- COLONEL HINOKI,
I HEAR THE N.S.A's BEEN
USING YOUR SERVICES
QUITE A BIT THESE DAYS.
IS THAT REGARDING
THE KASPER INCIDENT?
IF I WERE YOU,
I'D HEAD BACK TO THE BAHAMAS.
HANG WITH THIS CROWD
AND YOU'LL ONLY GET BURNED.
- ( laughs )
AH, N.C.S. EUROPEAN
CHEIF GEORGE BLACK,
THE INFAMOUS "BOOK MAN."
PRETTY CRASS READING FOR
SOMEONE OF YOUR STATURE.
- ( Black laughs )
- I OFFERED THE N.S.A.
ADVICE ON HOW TO RESPOND
TO THE GLOBAL GRID.
BUT THAT'S DONE.
I'M HEADING HOME NOW.
- OH, AND HOW WILL
THEY BE RESPONDING?
- HELL IF I KNOW.
( chuckles )
- THE HEKMATYAR GLOBAL GRID,
THAT'S A RELIEF.
AS USUAL, THE N.S.A's
BEHIND THE TIMES
AND BARKING UP
THE WRONG TREE.
THE REAL STORY RIGHT NOW
IS THIS LITTLE LADY.
- UM, NO.  NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
REALLY.  I PROMISE.
- I DOUBT THAT.
H.C.L.I's ACTIONS OF LATE
HAVE UPSET THE MILITARY.
THE N.S.A. WON'T ACT,
BUT I'M STILL WORRIED.
YOU SHOULD KEEP IN MIND,
MISS HEKMATYAR,
MY OPERATION WANTS
TO PROTECT YOU.
- DOES EVERYONE ON YOUR SIDE
SEE EVERY LITTLE THING
AS PART OF A CONSPIRACY?
PARANOIA ISN'T AN OPERATION.
- MY DEAR KOKO,
THIS MODERN WORLD
IS MADE OF CONSPIRACIES.
I DON'T EVEN
HAVE TIME TO SLEEP
BECAUSE PEOPLE LIKE YOU
WITH POWER
AND MONEY ARE OUT SKULKING
AROUND THE UNDERWORLD.
AT LEAST I STILL
HAVE TIME TO EAT.
YOU'VE BEEN ALL OVER
THE WORLD THESE DAYS.
OSAKA, TAIPEI, SHANGHAI,
SINGAPORE...
AND FROM WASHINGTON,
I'M GUESSING MIAMI'S NEXT.
WE BOTH CROSSED
A LINE IN THE SAND
A LONG TIME AGO.
BUT THE NEXT LINE
IS WHERE YOU GO FROM WORKING
WITHIN THE SYSTEM
TO TRYING TO DESTROY IT.
CROSS THAT AND I MIGHT NOT
BE ABLE TO HELP YOU ANYMORE.
JUST KEEP YOUR TEAM
AWAY FROM THE ENCLAVE.
- Koko: GOD,
THESE GUYS NEVER QUIT
WITH THE METAPHORS
AND CODE NAMES.
YOU GET ANY OF THAT,
JONAH, HUH?
- HM.
- YOU THINK STICKING
YOUR NOSE IN MY BUSINESS
AND DIGGING UP
THOSE LITTLE FACTS
IS GOING TO
HELP YOU PROTECT
YOUR PRECIOUS SYSTEM?
WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO SAVE, "BOOK MAN"?
WITH THE WHOLE WORLD HEADED DOWN
A STEEP DECLINE
IS THERE EVEN
A SYSTEM LEFT TO UPHOLD?
HERE'S A HYPOTHETICAL.
A UTOPIA APPEARS...
BUT YOU WON'T CELEBRATE IT.
YOU DEFEND
THE CURRENT WORLD-ORDER,
WHICH YOU SEE AS JUST.
CHANGE IS WHAT YOU FEAR.
AND ANYONE WHO PUSHES
FOR A NEW ORDER IS THE ENEMY.
IN YOUR MIND, IF YOU CANNOT
MAINTAIN THE STATUS QUO,
YOU'VE FAILED YOUR FRIENDS,
YOUR FAMILY,
AND YOUR COUNTRY.
- INTERESTING.
MAYBE I WOULD LIKE TO SEE
THIS NEW WORLD OF YOURS.
- WELL, AS I SAID,
IT WAS ONLY HYPOTHETICAL.
- Black: DID HINOKI
GO BACK TO THE BAHAMAS?
- Operative: NO, HE POSTPONED
HIS RETURN BY TWO DAYS.
OUR TAIL SAYS
HE LEFT DULLES.
- HE TOOK THE BAIT.  GOOD.
KEEP EYES
ON THE LITTLE LADY.
- ( phone beeps )
- I TELL THEM THAT,
BUT IF HER HISTORY'S
ANYTHING TO GO BY,
KOKO AND HER TEAM WILL
MANAGE TO LOSE OUR TAIL
THE SECOND THEY
GET OFF THE PLANE
AT MIAMI INTERNATIONAL.
- OH, CRAP-STICKS!
I THINK I JUST
LOST TEAM KOKO.
ONE MINUTE I'M BUYING
STONE CRAB TACOS,
NEXT MINUTE THEY'RE GONE.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO TELL SCARECROW?
- Scarecrow: ALL RIGHT,
STAY ON STANDBY.
- Schokolade: WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA YELL AT ME?
- NAH, ONCE THEY GOT OFF
THE PLANE IN MIAMI,
I DIDN'T REALLY FIGURE
WE'D BE ABLE TO STAY
ON THEIR TRAIL.
THEY'RE PROBABLY OUT AT SEA.
SHE'S AT HER BEST THERE.
- YEAH.
- GO STARE AT THE WAVES
AND EAT SOME MORE TACOS
UNTIL I GIVE YOU NEW ORDERS.
- ( dial tone )
- UH...
- Scarecrow: 50 BUCKS
SAYS KOKO'S HEADING TO CUBA.
- Black: GUANTANAMO BAY
NAVAL BASE,
AMERICA'S LITTLE
PATCH OF CUBA--
AN ENCLAVE.
- Hopkins:
KOKO HEKMATYAR'S RECENT ACTIONS
INDICATE SHE'S GATHERING PARTS
FOR SOMETHING BIG.
SHE'S ALREADY PARTNERED
WITH FOUR ADVANCED
NANO MANUFACTURING FIRMS
IN ASIA.
AND WHEN YOU FIGURE IN
HER KIDNAPPING
OF DR. BABURIN,
ALL SIGNS POINT
TO HER BUILDING
A QUANTUM COMPUTER.
- THAT'S SCIENCE FICTION.
- MAYBE.
BUT THINK ABOUT IT, SIR.
WE MAY NOT HAVE
FLYING CARS OR JET PACKS,
BUT SOME OF
THE TECH WE HAVE NOW
WOULD'VE FELT LIKE THAT
JUST A DECADE AGO.
- BUT QUANTUM COMPUTERS?
THE BEST SCIENTISTS
IN THE WORLD
SAY THEY'RE STILL
20 YEARS OUT.
AND THAT'S IF EVERYTHING
BREAKS OUR WAY.
- THOSE SCIENTISTS ARE
CONSERVATIVE PENCIL PUSHERS.
DR. MINAMI AMADA IS AMONG
THE WORLD'S TOP ROBOTICISTS
AND HER UNORTHODOX THEORIES
ARE REVOLUTIONIZING
COMPUTER ENGINEERING AS WELL.
I BELIEVE SHE
AND HER BEST FRIEND KOKO
HAVE BEEN PLANNING THIS
SINCE THEY WERE 18.
IT'S INCREDIBLE
THEY'VE MANAGED
TO KEEP THEIR PROJECT A SECRET
ALL THESE YEARS.
BUT NOW THAT THEY'RE
IN THE BUILDING STAGE,
TOO MUCH EVIDENCE POINTS
TO A QUANTUM COMPUTER
BEING THEIR FOCUS.
AND IF THEY'VE MADE
AS MUCH PROGRESS AS I SUSPECT,
IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER
IF WE'VE CAUGHT ON.
OF COURSE, ALL OF THIS
IS STILL JUST CONJECTURE.
- IF YOU ARE RIGHT,
WHAT HAPPENS
IF THEY COMPLETE
THE COMPUTER?
- IN THEORY,
A QUANTUM COMPUTER TAKES SECONDS
TO CALCULATE SOMETHING
THAT TAKES THE LATEST
SUPER-COMPUTER AT LEAST
THOUSANDS OF YEARS.
ALL OF THE ENCRYPTION,
PASSWORDS,
AND SECURITY ALGORITHMS
THAT PROTECT OUR GOVERNMENT
SERVERS AND DEVICES
COULD BE CRACKED
LIKE AN EGG.
AND AS FAR
AS WEAPONS CONTROL,
OUR MISSILES ARE NOT
FULLY AUTOMATED.
WE STILL KEEP MAN
IN THE LOOP.
BUT IN A LAUNCH SITUATION,
THAT CAPACITY FOR HUMAN ERROR
COULD BE ELIMINATED.
- NOW, THAT SOUNDS LIKE
SCIENCE FICTION.
KOKO HEKMATYAR
PASSED THROUGH DULLES
SO I INTERCEPTED HER.
- Operative: HOW IS SHE?
- EVEN MORE SLIPPERY
THAN I THOUGHT.
LET'S PREPARE FOR THE WORST
SO WE DON'T GET BLINDSIDED.
SHE CONFRONTED ME TO SHOW ME
JUST HOW SERIOUS SHE IS.
THEN SHE VANISHED IN MIAMI.
BUT I'M CERTAIN HER NEXT TARGET
IS GUANTANAMO BAY.
- DO YOU THINK...
SHE'S AFTER
CHATTY RABBIT'S FOOT?
- SURE SEEMS LIKE IT.
- BUT THAT MEANS
THEY'LL BE MAKING A MOVE
ON "CAMP NO."
AND SECURITY THERE IS EVEN
TIGHTER THAN AT CAMP DELTA.
- I KNOW.  I THREW RABBIT'S FOOT
DOWN THAT HOLE.
IF I HADN'T,
WE'D HAVE
A NEW JULIAN ASSANGE
ON OUR HANDS.
- IBRAHIM FAIZA, A.K.A.
"CHATTY RABBIT'S FOOT,"
IS AN EGYPTIAN NATIONAL,
AGE 39.
HE'S A POLITICAL DISSIDENT,
HACKER, AND INTERNET SENSATION
WHO ALSO HAPPENS TO HAVE
DOCTORATE IN QUANTUM PHYSICS.
HE WAS BORN INTO
A WEALTHY FAMILY
AND WAS EDUCATED
AT CAMBRIDGE.
WHILE THERE, HE FIRST BECAME
INTERESTED IN POLITICS
AND WROTE A THESIS ENTITLED,
"SOCIAL REVOLUTION
THROUGH INFORMATION."
AFTER GRADUATION,
HE ASSUMED A POSITION
AT THE WESTERN THEORETICAL
PHYSICS LABORATORY.
AT THE SAME TIME,
HE LAUNCHED HIS
"INFORMATION REVOLUTION
NETWORK" ONLINE,
WHICH PROMPTLY
THREW THE INTERNET
AND ARAB STREETS
INTO CHAOS.
THROUGH HIS
HACKING, HE'D FIND
AND THEN POST SECRET DOCUMENTS
BEFORE VANISHING DOWN
THE PROVERBIAL HOLE,
WHICH EARNED HIM
THE RABBIT'S FOOT NAME.
- Black: MINOR CORRECTION.
- LEILA IBRAHIM FAIZA.
CHATTY RABBIT'S FOOT
IS A WOMAN, AGE 28.
HERE'S THE CAMP NO
LIVE-FEED.
- Lady: CAMP NO?
- Hopkins: THE CAMP NO
DETAINMENT CENTER.
THAT PLACE IS SO FAR BEYOND
TOP-SECRET.
THE ADMINISTRATION WON'T
EVEN CONFIRM ITS EXISTENCE.
WHAT THE--
- I'M BORED OF THE SEGWAY.
I THINK I'LL PLAY A GAME.
- THAT'S CHATTY RABBIT'S FOOT.
SHE'S HELD UNDER
DIFFERENT CONDITIONS
THAN OTHER PRISONERS.
THIS IS TOP-SECRET.
AND WHILE WE'RE
CHECKING IN ON THINGS,
WE HAVE A GLOBAL HAWK
FLYING RIGHT OVER
THE NEW MARCHEN FACTORY.
- Male Operative: WHAT?!
HANG ON, THEY'VE
GOT A HOT SPRING?
- Female operative:
WE'RE USING A DRONE
TO PLAY PEEPING-TOM?!
- ( man laughs )
- Black: THE BODYGUARD,
KAREN LOW; DR. MINAMI AMADA--
WAIT, WHO'S THE BLONDE?
- Man: MAYBE ELENA BABURIN.
CAN WE GET A BETTER ANGLE?
EACH ONE OF THESE WOMEN
REMINDS ME OF A DIFFERENT
ANIMAL IN HUMAN SKIN.
I SEE A FOX, A RACCOON,
AND A RABBIT.
- ( laughs )
- ( loud whirring )
- Kasper: HUH? KOKO DID WHAT?!
SPEAK UP.  I CAN'T HEAR
A WORD YOU'RE SAYING.
SHE WENT TO AMERICA WITHOUT
CHECKING IN AT HEADQUARTERS?
WAS THIS INFORMATION
REALLY WORTH ALL THE TROUBLE
OF A SATELLITE CALL?
NO, I'M NOT SURPRISED
SHE DIDN'T REPORT IN.
LOOK, I'M BUSY.
I GOT TO JET.
GEEZ, OF COURSE
KOKO'S NOT GONNA STOP IN
AT THE MAIN OFFICE.
- WHAT MAKES YOU
SAY THAT, KASPER?
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
SHE HATES OUR FATHER,
CAN'T EVEN STAND TO BE
IN THE SAME ROOM WITH HIM.
- NOW THAT MIGHT MAKE KOKO
SEEM IMMATURE,
BUT I THINK IT'S
PERFECTLY REASONABLE.
AND IT'S NOT
THE "REFUSING TO CHECK IN"
STUFF THAT THEY'RE
REALLY UPSET ABOUT.
I'M SURE THEY'RE
JUST NERVOUS
ABOUT WHATEVER
SHE'S DOING IN AMERICA.
- HMM, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY ABOUT FLOYD.
HE RAISED HIS OWN CHILDREN
TO PROFIT FROM WAR.
AND YET AFTER HE RESCUED ME,
I GUARDED HIM FOR YEARS.
IN ALL THAT TIME, I NEVER WAS
ABLE TO UNDERSTAND
HIS TRUE MOTIVATIONS.
- IF I HAD TO CHOOSE,
I'D SIDE WITH KOKO.
TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST,
I CAN'T STAND
H.C.L.I's NEW DIRECTION.
- WOW, YOU SURE?
- I'M POSITIVE.
WHAT IS THE GLOBAL GRID
REALLY ABOUT?
THE HOME OFFICE IS GONNA
BE RUNNING THE WHOLE SHEBANG.
RIGHT? SO WHAT THE HELL USE
WILL THEY HAVE FOR US DEALERS?
I MEAN,
I LOVE MY JOB AS IS.
GETTING TO TRAVEL THE WORLD
WITH YOU AND
THE REST OF THE GUYS,
IT'S AWESOME.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT MY SISTER THINKS
OF OUR LINE OF WORK.
AND LIKE MY FATHER,
I DON'T CARE.
BUT LISTEN, H.C.L.I.
MAY CHANGE ITS MODEL,
BUT ARMS DEALERS
ARE NECESSARY.
WE START WARS WHEN
IT'S CONVENIENT.
AND WHEN IT'S NOT,
WE DO OUR PART
TO MAINTAIN THE PEACE.
I GLAD WE AT LEAST
SOLD THOSE S.A.Ms TODAY.
- Chequita: ME TOO.
LET'S ALL GO OUT
FOR BARBEQUE TONIGHT.
- Kasper: ABSOLUTELY!
NO, FORGET THAT.
WE'RE THROWING A PARTY.
SKY'S THE FREAKING LIMIT.
- ( cheering )
- ( car brakes screech )
- BA-- BA-- BANG, BANG.  BANG.
- Wilee: SMOKE.  BOOM-BOOM.
FLASH!
- Tojo: POP.  PA-- POP!
- OKAY, GUYS.
GOOD WORK.
LET'S GET SOME DINNER!
- All: 'KAY.
- Lutz: KOKO?
- YES?
- THIS DRILL-- WE'RE PREPPING
FOR ANOTHER EXTRACTION,
AREN'T WE? SO WHO DO YOU
HAVE US KIDNAPPING THIS TIME?
- LET'S JUST SAY YOU'LL BE
GETTING SOMEONE WHO'S
ESSENTIAL TO MY PLANS.
IF THIS MAKES YOU
UNCOMFORTABLE,
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO COME ALONG.
- NO, I'M IN.
YOU HIRED ME
TO BE A PROFESSIONAL.
I'LL GO WHERE
YOU TELL ME TO.
BUT I HAVE NOTICED
THE KINDS OF MISSIONS WE RUN
LATELY HAVE CHANGED A LOT.
ALL DUE RESPECT.
- WORRYING ABOUT THOSE
KINDS OF THINGS IS MY JOB.
THE PERSON WE'RE EXTRACTING
IS SOMEONE WE ALL NEED.
OUR MEANS MAY HAVE CHANGED SOME,
BUT OUR ENDS ARE THE SAME.
LOOK, I GET HOW A FORMER COP
WOULD BE BOTHERED BY KIDNAPPING.
TO BE HONEST,
I'M A BIT SURPRISED
YOU HADN'T BROUGHT YOUR CONCERNS
TO ME SOONER THAN THIS.
I CAN'T SAY THINGS'LL GO BACK
TO HOW THEY WERE.
ALL I CAN SAY FOR NOW
IS TRUST ME, LUTZ.
- OKAY.
I'LL TRUST YOU, LITTLE LADY.
- HOW ABOUT EVERYONE ELSE?
ARE YOU GUYS STILL IN?
I WON'T BE HURT
IF YOU'RE NOT.
- I'M IN.
MISSION SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
- DON'T EVEN BOTHER ASKING.
YOU KNOW I'M ALWAYS
BEHIND YOU, KOKO...
AND IN FRONT OF YOU,
AND ON TOP.
I MEAN, COME ON, LUTZ.
DID THEY SHOOT YOU IN THE ASS
OR BLOW YOUR DAMN BALLS OFF?
- I'M IN FOR DAMN SURE.
- OH, HELL YEAH.
- SAME HERE.
- BE MY PLEASURE.
- I AM TOO.
- THANK YOU.
YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST!
NOW LET'S GO GET
SOMETHING TO EAT!
- All: 'KAY.
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Man: MR. HINOKI,
SO NICE TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
COMMANDER PLAME, U.S. NAVY.
I JUST GOT IN
FROM BELTSVILLE
WHERE I'M CURRENTLY
SERVING AS CHIEF
OF THE SPECIAL
COLLECTIONS UNIT, G.Z.
- IT'S A PLEASURE,
BUT I AM JUST A CONSULTANT.
- HEY, NOW, DON'T
SELL YOURSELF SHORT.
YOU WERE JAPAN'S
GREAT SPYMASTER.
THIS IS QUITE
THE HONOR FOR ME.
I HEAR YOU'RE
ADVISING WEBSTER.
STILL LIKE GETTING
YOUR HANDS DIRTY, HUH?
THAT'S GOOD BECAUSE
WEBSTER'S PUT ME
IN CHARGE
OF A BIG NEW CASE.
HE'S LIKE FOR YOU
TO GIVE YOUR THOUGHTS
ON MY REPORT.
WE HAVE GOOD INTEL
THAT AN IDENTIFIED
GROUP'S PLANNING AN ATTACK
TO RECOVER A HIGH-VALUE ASSET
FROM GUANTANAMO BAY.
THIS INTEL CAME DOWN
FROM A VERY RELIABLE SOURCE.
UNFORTUNATELY,
I AM NOT AT LIBERTY
TO REVEAL WHOM
AT THIS MOMENT.
- HIS SOURCE HAS
TO BE BOOK MAN.
BUT HE SAID
IT "CAME DOWN" TO HIM,
IMPLYING BOOK MAN'S NETWORK
REACHES AS HIGH
AS THE PRESIDENT'S
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR.
INCREDIBLE.  BOOK MAN'S
TAKEN ME OUT OF THE LOOP
THAT EASILY AND
I CAN'T TOUCH HIM.
THE MAJOR GENERAL
CLEARLY WANTS NO PART
IN WHAT THIS HAS BECOME.
I TOOK THE BAIT
AND THAT FAT WEASEL
REELED ME RIGHT IN.
THAT SOUNDS TROUBLING.
HOW DO YOU PLAN ON
STOPPING THIS GROUP--
THAT IS, IF YOU'RE
ALLOWED TO TELL ME?
- TECHNICALLY, NO,
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO SAY,
BUT YOU HAVE CLEARANCE.
GIVEN HER RECENT ACTIONS
BOTH REAL AND RUMORED,
WE BELIEVE KOKO HEKMATYAR
IS BEHIND THIS
PLANNED EXTRACTION.
WE'RE CERTAIN
SHE'S AFTER THE HACKER
WHO GOES BY THE ALIAS
"CHATTY RABBIT'S FOOT,"
CURRENTLY HELD
IN THE CAMP NO FACILITY.
CAMP NO IS A BLACK SITE--
OFF ANY GOVERNMENT MAP.
AND RABBIT'S FOOT IS
ITS MOST PRIZED POSSESSION.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE'LL HAVE
TO MOVE HER OUT OF THERE
BEFORE HEKMATYAR
CAN STRIKE.
THIS ACTION
WILL BE PROTECTED
BY A HIGHLY ARMED
AND TRAINED ESCORT
CHARGED WITH ELIMINATING
HEKMATYAR'S TEAM
SHOULD THEY MANAGE TO INTERSECT
RABBIT'S FOOT EN ROUTE.
YOU MAY HAVE HEARD
OF THIS ESCORT BEFORE.
THEY WERE PREVIOUSLY ATTACHED
TO THE NAVY'S
SPECIAL WARFARE COMMAND
IN AFGHANISTAN.
SEAL TEAM NINE,
CODE NAME: NIGHT NINE.
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪