- Lutz: JONAH.
HEY, JONAH!
DAMN, I LOST HIM.
YEAH, OF COURSE I LOST HIM.
THE KID WAS STATIONED WITH
AN ALPINE UNIT. I WAS A COP.
THOUGH I WAS WITH A PRESTIGIOUS
ANTI-TERRORIST TASK FORCE.
- Valmet: THIS IS
A HIGH-PRESSURE PAINTBALL GUN.
GETTIN' TAGGED BY ONE HURTS.
- YEAH, I KNOW ALL ABOUT 'EM.
SO, WHAT?  YOU WANT ME
TO TRAIN WITH THAT?
- YOU'RE DAMN STRAIGHT, LUTZ.
PRETTY SURE YOU WERE THE ONLY
ONE TO GET HIT BY ENEMY FIRE--
- ( laughs ) BETTER HIM THAN ME.
- SERIOUSLY.
- TIME FOR A NICE GAME
OF CAPTURE THE FLAG.
YOU AND JONAH--
FIRST TO THE FLAG WINS ALL.
- DO I HAVE TO?
I DON'T WANNA SHOOT AT LUTZ.
- ALL RIGHT,
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU GET 15 POINTS
FOR EACH SHOT THAT HITS.
AND 30 IF YOU'RE THE FIRST ONE
TO THE FLAG.
AT THE END, I'LL GIVE YOU
A SPECIAL MEAL TICKET
FOR EVERY 50 POINTS YOU SCORE.
NOW, LET'S GO, JONAH.
- Tojo: THAT'S ABOUT
AS EASY AS MATH GETS.
- YOU'RE A GOOD SHOT, LUTZ.
NONE OF US DOUBT THAT.
YOU JUST GOTTA LEARN
MOUNTAIN COMBAT.
COMMENCE OPERATION.
- Lutz:
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO,
WITH EVERYBODY GIVING ME
SO MUCH SHIT?
- WIDE OPEN.
- KEEP GETTIN' FLASHES
OF MY SNIPER WORK
SPINNING AROUND MY HEAD.
THE TIMES I TOOK THE SHOT
AND THE TIMES I DIDN'T.
THAT ASSASSIN FROM ORCHESTRA.
AM I A FAILURE 'CAUSE I
COULDN'T SHOOT A LITTLE GIRL?
I WAS TRAINED
FOR SNIPING THUGS
WHO HAVE THEIR GUNS
POINTED AT HOSTAGES,
OR TERRORISTS WHO'VE GOT THEIR
FINGER ON A BOMB SWITCH.
THE SKILLS I LEARNED AS A COP
LET ME BLOW THE BRAINS
OUT OF THE WORLD'S SCUM
BEFORE THEY CAN BLINK AN EYE.
NOBODY EVER TRAINED ME
TO SHOOT KIDS.
BUT IF I HAD IT TO DO AGAIN,
IF ANOTHER CHICK LIKE THE ONE
FROM ORCHESTRA SHOWED UP
AND THREATENED
THE BOSS LADY'S LIFE,
COULD I HANDLE THAT?
COULD I MAKE THAT SPLIT-SECOND
DECISION TO SHOOT HER DEAD?
PROBABLY.
I RESPECT KOKO,
AND I WANT TO PROTECT HER.
STILL, WHAT IF THE KID
I HAD TO SHOOT
LOOKED JUST LIKE JONAH?
AHHH!
- ( laughs )
- JONAH!
I'M GONNA KILL YOU!
DAMN IT, GET BACK HERE!
- ( laughs )
- HA HA! CATCHIN' UP!
OW!
THE HELL?
A TRAP?
AHH!
AW, SHIT!
NOOOO!
- Valmet:
TWO, THREE, FOUR...
- THAT'S MY LUTZ.
YOU NEVER LET ME DOWN.
- ...NINE...
- LAUGH IT UP.
IT WAS JUST A GAME.
IT'S NOT LIKE
I WAS REALLY TRYING.
- News anchor:
TERRITORY DISPUTES STILL HAVE
TENSIONS RUNNING HIGH BETWEEN
MIDDLE EASTERN COUNTRY A
AND EUROPEAN COUNTRY B.
AN INTERNATIONAL COMMUNICATIONS
COMPANY REPORTS
THAT COUNTRY A'S
MILITARY HAS GATHERED
AT THE LINE OF CONFLICT--
- VALMET, COME ON.
IT'S TIME TO GET UP.
- OH, GOOD MORNING.
DON'T WE HAVE A MEETING
ON THE AGENDA TODAY?
- YES.
THE UNMANNED AERIAL VEHICLE
SUPPLY COMMITTEE
IS MEETING AT
COUNTRY B'S EMBASSY IN LONDON.
- THIS COMMITTEE IS DEDICATED
TO INTRODUCING
UNMANNED AERIAL VEHICLES AT
LAST TO COUNTRY B'S AIR FORCE.
WE WILL BE LOOKING AT H.C.L.I.'S
AMERICAN-MADE PREDATOR
AND THE EURO GROUP'S
NEURON PROJECT--
- DID YOU CHECK OUT
WHO THE COMPETITION'S
THROWING AT US TODAY?
- Koko: WOW.
- AMALIA TOROHOVSKY--
ACTRESS TURNED ARMS DEALER.
- SHE'S BEAUTIFUL, HUH?
- ( Russian accent )
KOKO HEKMATYAR!
MY GOODNESS, WHAT A PLEASURE.
I HEARD THERE WAS
GOING TO BE
A SWEET, FRESH-FACED
DEALER HERE TODAY
AND I SIMPLY
HAD TO SEE FOR MYSELF.
SO THE RUMORS ARE TRUE.
DO GO EASY ON ME.
- OH, SURE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Koko: THIS SUCKS.
A LOT.
LISTEN TO THIS, JONAH.
- I DON'T THINK TELLING ME
WILL MAKE IT ANY BETTER.
- I'M GOING TO ANYWAY.
( laughs )
THE COMPETITION IS FORMIDABLE
ON THIS TRIP.
IT'S LIKE THE DEAL HAD ALREADY
BEEN MADE BY THE TIME I ARRIVED,
LIKE I'D BEEN
TAKEN OUT OF THE GAME
BEFORE I EVEN STARTED TO PLAY.
THE RUMORS WERE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT WOMAN.
SHE MOVES FAST.
- WHAT WOMAN?
- OH, THIS MEGA-HOT ACTRESS
TURNED ARMS DEALER.
ALL SHE HAS TO DO
IS CROOK HER FINGER
AND THOSE
OLD MILITARY BOYS
COME RUNNING
TO BUY HER MERCHANDISE.
HER FAME LANDED HER
A WEALTHY HUSBAND,
BUT HER STAR FADED,
HE PASSED AWAY,
AND HIS ENTIRE FORTUNE
WENT TO HER.
SO NOW SHE'S USING
HER CONSIDERABLE CHARM
TO WORK HER WAY UP
IN THE WEAPONS TRADE.
SHE DOES SEEM LIKE A WEIRD ONE,
THOUGH.
FEW ROUNDS SHORT
OF A FULL CLIP.
- WHAT PRODUCT DO YOU HAVE
ON THE TABLE NOW?
- BRAND NEW U.A.V.s--
RADIO-CONTROLLED PLANES
USED FOR SCOUTING
AND RECONNAISSANCE.
THESE BABIES NEVER GET TIRED
OR CARELESS.
AND NOBODY DIES
IF ONE GETS SHOT DOWN.
WHEN EQUIPPED WITH WEAPONS,
IT CAN EVEN BE USED IN COMBAT.
JUST RECENTLY,
IN FACT, ONE WAS USED
TO BOMB A CERTAIN ORGANIZATION.
WE ARE LIVING IN
AN AGE WHERE ROBOTS
ARE USED TO KILL HUMANS.
I'M SURE ISAAC ASIMOV
IS ROLLING IN HIS GRAVE.
- I'M NOT SURE I LIKE THE SOUND
OF THOSE THINGS.
- HEY, I'M WITH YOU
ON THAT PART.
THEY CREEP ME OUT TOO.
BUT MY JOB
IS TO SELL THE SUCKERS,
REGARDLESS OF
MY PERSONAL FEELINGS.
- HEY, KOKO!
UGH, THIS PLACE.
IT'S FREAKIN' HUMID
AND THE SKY'S ALWAYS CLOUDY
AND THE FOOD IS DISGUSTING.
- Koko: BE NICE.
- YEAH SO,
ABOUT THIS WHOLE
PREDATOR SITUATION,
THE AMERICANS
ARE NOT INTERESTED.
LET ME SEE
IF I'VE GOT YOUR BASIC IDEA.
THE U.S. SELLS U.A.V.s
TO COUNTRY A
WITH THE UNDERSTANDING
THAT THEY'LL BE USED
TO SETTLE CIVIL UNREST.
THIS, IN TURN, WILL PISS OFF
NEIGHBORING COUNTRY B,
AT WHICH POINT THE U.S. WILL
OFFER TO SELL TO THEM AS WELL.
TO MAINTAIN THE BALANCE
OF POWER, RIGHT?
YOUR PLAN
HAS ONE MINOR FLAW, THOUGH.
COUNTRY B
IS ALREADY IN THE PROCESS
OF DEVELOPING THEIR OWN U.A.V.s
WITH THE NEURON PROJECT.
THE AMERICANS FIGURE
THIS WILL RESOLVE ITSELF
ON ITS OWN WITHOUT THEIR HELP.
- THE U.A.V. MARKET
IS JUST GONNA KEEP
GETTING HOTTER AND HOTTER.
IT'S ALWAYS BETTER TO BE
THE ONE FEEDING THE FIRE
THAN GETTING BURNED BY IT,
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- I GOTTA GET GOING.
YOU KNOW SCARECROW.
HE'LL PISS HIMSELF IF I SPEND
TOO MUCH TIME WITH YOU.
- HMM.
- WHA-- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I FIND IT INTERESTING
THAT A C.I.A. TECHIE
WOULD JOIN UP WITH SCARECROW.
HIS CRUSADE AGAINST ME
IS PATHETIC.
BUT THAT'S OKAY,
I WON'T STOP YOU.
IN FACT, I THINK YOU AND I ARE
GOING TO GET ALONG QUITE WELL.
- UM, THIS--
THIS CAN'T BE A--
OH, HOLY CRAP, IT IS.
AWESOME!
IS IT FOR ME?
- I DON'T WANT THE AMERICANS
PULLING OUT OF THIS DEAL,
SO YOU'LL KEEP AN EYE ON THEM
FOR ME, RIGHT?
- SHE'S TOTALLY USING ME.
I'M PROBABLY GETTING MYSELF
INTO AN UGLY SITUATION.
OH, WELL, WHATEV.
SURE.
- Koko:
UGO, LET'S SWING BY THE HOTELS
THAT ARE ACCOMMODATING
COUNTRY B'S PEOPLE.
- YOU GOT IT.
- GET READY TO ROCK, BOYS!
WE'VE GOT STUFF TO SELL.
- DAMN.
LITTLE LADY'S ON FIRE TODAY.
- MS. KOKO HEKMATYAR
OF H.C.L.I.?
IF YOU'LL WAIT IN THE LOBBY,
PLEASE.
- ( door dings )
- GENERA-- OH!
- MS. HEKMATYAR.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU CAN SEE
HOW THINGS STAND.
SORRY.
- ( chuckles )
- Man: MY APOLOGIES,
MS. HEKMATYAR.
I KNOW YOU WERE
SCHEDULED TO MEET WITH
THE COLONEL THIS AFTERNOON,
BUT I'M AFRAID
HE HAS BEEN
UNAVOIDABLY DETAINED.
- RIGHT.
- Man #2: I AM VERY SORRY.
THE LIEUTENANT GENERAL
HAS ALREADY LEFT.
HE'LL BE GONE FOR THE DAY.
- LOVELY.
- Man #3: INITIALLY,
I WAS ONE OF THE ONES
PUSHING FOR THE PREDATORS.
IN THE END,
THE EURO GROUP
WON ME OVER, THOUGH.
WE NEED TO STICK
WITH EUROPEAN TECHNOLOGY.
- OF COURSE.
( grunting )
THAT BITCH
IS EVERYWHERE!
- SEEN HER GET HER PANTIES
IN A TWIST, BUT HER WHOLE BODY?
- REMINDS ME
OF RODIN'S THE THINKER.
- ONE PLACE LEFT.
LET'S ROLL.
- Ugo: WHO IS IT?
- LIEUTENANT COLONEL MARQUIS
FROM COUNTRY B'S ARMY.
HE'S BEEN A SUPPORTER
OF THE PREDATORS.
AND HE'S WORKED WITH US BEFORE.
- MS. TOROHOVSKY PAID ME A VISIT
EARLIER AS WELL,
BUT I HAVE WITHHELD
MAKING A DECISION.
- I APPRECIATE THAT.
- YOU COULD TAKE IT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
MAYBE SHE'S MOVING QUICKLY
BECAUSE SHE KNOWS
YOU'RE A WORTHY OPPONENT.
I IMAGINE H.C.L.I. HEADQUARTERS
HAS ALREADY INFORMED YOU,
BUT AN ITALIAN NEWSPAPER
WROTE AN EXPOSE
ON YOUR IMPORTATION PLAN.
- THE NEWSPAPER IS REALLY
NOTHING BETTER THAN A TABLOID.
- IF THIS DOESN'T WORK,
WE'LL LEAK THE INFO
TO A LEGITIMATE PAPER
AND FINISH HER OFF.
- Amalia: KOKO WAS SMART.
SAYING THE PREDATORS
ACQUIRED HAD BEEN DISPOSED OF
BY THE ITALIAN AIR FORCE
AND INSISTING THAT THE U.S.
WAS NOT DIRECTLY
PROVIDING THE AIRCRAFTS.
SHE HELPS COUNTRY A SAVE FACE
BY MAKING IT LOOK
LIKE CIVILIANS MADE THE DEAL.
- HEKMATYAR'S
FANCY FOOTWORK IS HER
MAIN STRENGTH IN THIS GAME.
HOWEVER, YOUR CHARM
AND CONNECTIONS
PROVED TO BE
SUPERIOR THIS TIME.
- Lutz: NOW THAT'S A POSE
THAT INSPIRES CONFIDENCE.
- IT IS. IT'S LIKE SHE'S
STARING ADVERSITY IN THE FACE,
REFUSING TO GIVE UP.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
- SO, IS THAT IT THEN?
WE DONE?
- OF COURSE NOT.
I'VE PLANTED
THE NECESSARY SEEDS.
NOW WE JUST WAIT FOR THEM
TO BEAR FRUIT.
I WILL OUTWIT THAT WOMAN.
IT'S WHAT I DO.
AND FORTUNATELY,
I'M VERY GOOD AT IT.
- R: WILL SHE BE OKAY?
WE'RE JUST LEAVING VALMET,
WILEE, AND LUTZ HERE
IN ENGLAND WITH HER.
- I'M NOT REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT IT.
LET'S JUST CONCENTRATE
ON GETTING OUR OWN WORK DONE.
- Mao: WE'LL NEED
TO KEEP OUR GUARD UP.
SEE THOSE SUITS OVER THERE?
EURO GROUP'S GIVEN US A TAIL.
- R: REALLY?
- SHE'LL BE FINE WITH
THE OTHER THREE.
HAVE A LITTLE FAITH
IN YOUR CREW MEMBERS' ABILITIES.
- SO BASICALLY,
EVERYTHING WILL BE A-OKAY
AS LONG AS I CAN CLOSE THE DEAL
WITH COUNTRY B
QUICKLY AND EFFECTIVELY.
- ( all laugh )
- All: NAH, NEVER HAPPEN.
- Lehm: THAT'S EVEN GIVING KOKO
A HARD TIME.
- Valmet ( thinking ):
SHE'S BEEN LIKE THIS
EVER SINCE THE
NEGOTIATIONS TWO DAYS AGO.
I'M STARTING TO GET
A LITTLE WORRIED.
CAREFUL, KOKO.
KEEP EATING ALL THAT CRAP
AND NOT EXERCISING
AND YOU'RE GONNA GET FAT.
- IT'D BE COOL IF IT WOULD
ALL JUST GO TO MY BOOBS
AND I COULD HAVE
A CHEST LIKE YOURS.
- OH, NO! YOU'RE PERFECT
JUST THE WAY YOU ARE, REALLY.
- ( Koko laughs )
OH, STOP.
- LOOKS LIKE SHE'S SENT
ANOTHER EMAIL.
- THAT BRINGS THE TOTAL
TO 25 IN ONE HOUR.
- HA!  DO YOU THINK
WE COULD CRACK THEM
WITH THE HELP OF AMALIA'S
FRIENDS AT THE D.G.S.E.?
- Man: THE FRENCH
SECURITY ORGANIZATION?
YEAH, PROBABLY.
BUT EVEN THEN,
IT WOULD TAKE A HUGE
AMOUNT OF TIME.
HAVEN'T WE PRETTY MUCH
WON ALREADY ANYWAY?
THERE'S NOTHING H.C.L.I.
CAN DO NOW. WHY WORRY?
- WE'LL SEE WHAT AMALIA THINKS.
KEEP INTERCEPTING HER MESSAGES.
- KOKO HERE.
SCHOKOLADE?
IT'S BAD.
VERY BAD.
YEP, IT'S LOOKING LIKE
I'VE LOST THE BATTLE
OVER THESE U.A.V. SALES.
MY PLAN WAS TO SEND
THE PREDATORS TO COUNTRY B
VIA ITALY TO AVOID
PROVOKING COUNTRY A.
BUT THE ITALIAN PRESS
CAUGHT WIND OF WHAT I WAS UP TO.
MS. TOROHOVSKY MUST HAVE PULLED
ALL THE RIGHT STRINGS.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT
FOR ME TO DO NOW.
H.C.L.I. IS OFFICIALLY
PULLING OUT OF THIS DEAL.
I WILL DROP BY TO SAY HELLO
AT TOMORROW'S VOTE, THOUGH.
- ( laughs )
AT TIMES LIKE THIS, I REMEMBER
WHY IT WASN'T DIFFICULT
TO LEAVE MY ACTING CAREER
BEHIND.
DON'T GET ME WRONG,
THEATER IS A BEAUTIFUL ART FORM,
ONE THAT IS WELL WORTH
DEDICATING ONE'S LIFE TO.
BUT NO MATTER HOW GOOD YOU ARE,
AT THE END OF THE DAY
IT'S JUST STILL MAKE-BELIEVE.
I WANTED SOMETHING
MORE THAN THAT, SO I QUIT.
FORTUNATELY, I DISCOVERED
THAT THE ARMS TRADE
IS FULL OF ACTORS.
YOU ARE CONSTANTLY TRYING
TO DECEIVE SOMEONE,
AND IF THEY SEE
THROUGH YOUR PRETENSE,
THE CONSEQUENCES ARE REAL.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I THINK IS HAPPENING HERE?
KOKO'S BEEN TRYING
HER HAND AT ACTING
DURING THOSE PHONE CALLS
YOU TAPPED.
THAT'S RIGHT. THE WOMAN IS--
- A LIAR!
- I THOUGHT YOU'D ACTUALLY
GIVEN UP. YOU HAD ME CONVINCED.
- I HOPE THEY ARE.
WE'LL FIND OUT SOON ENOUGH.
- Schokolade: JEEZ, MAKE ME
WADE THROUGH ALL THAT BULLSHIT
BEFORE YOU FINALLY SEND ME
A LEGIT EMAIL?
MAN, WHY IS IT I ALWAYS
SEEM TO END UP
WORKIN' FOR SLAVE DRIVERS?
A SINGLE DIAMOND
IS NOT WORTH ALL THIS WORK.
- Amalia: UNFORTUNATELY,
WE STILL DON'T KNOW
WHO IS THAT WOMAN
MEETING WITH HER.
WHATEVER THE CASE, KOKO'S GOT
A MASSIVE ATTACK PLANNED.
WHAT SHE WANTS IS TO TEAR APART
MY WEB OF ALLIANCES.
THAT SEEMS TO BE
FIGHTING STYLE SHE PREFERS.
I WILL SEND
THE COUNTRY B EXECS A REMINDER.
WHATEVER HAPPENS NEXT,
I DO NOT WANT THEM
CHANGING THEIR MINDS.
- ( knocking )
- Lutz: BOSS LADY?
CAN I COME IN?
- OF COURSE, LUTZ.
- HAVE YOU SEEN THE NEWS?
COUNTRY A
HAS DROPPED THAT CAMPAIGN
THAT THE AMERICANS
WERE SO UPSET ABOUT.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
YOU WERE HOPING WOULD HAPPEN.
SEEMS MIGHTY TIMELY,
DOESN'T IT?
- I COULDN'T MANIPULATE
A MILITARY OP LIKE THAT
FROM A HOTEL ROOM.
MY IDEA WAS SIMPLY A COG
IN A MUCH GREATER MACHINE.
IT TAKES THOUSANDS
UPON THOUSANDS OF COGS
TO MAKE UP AN ARMY.
AND IT'S THE HEARTS AND MINDS
OF THE PEOPLE
THAT ULTIMATELY
SET THOSE COGS IN MOTION.
THE WORLD IS SET ABLAZE
BY THE WILL OF ITS PEOPLE.
- Marquis: YOU'RE A
PERFECTIONIST, AREN'T YOU,
MS. TOROHOVSKY?
THE FIGHT IS ESSENTIALLY OVER.
AND YOU CAME OUT ON TOP.
SO WHAT NEED
COULD YOU POSSIBLY HAVE
TO WIN ME OVER AT THIS POINT?
- PARDON ME, LIEUTENANT COLONEL.
I HAVE A MESSAGE FOR YOU.
- HMM?
WHAT THE--
- IS SOMETHING AMISS?
- IT SEEMS THE GERMAN AIR FORCE
IS PURCHASING PREDATORS
FROM THE U.S.
A FULL 20 OF THEM!
AND THEY'RE ALL EQUIPPED
WITH GERMAN-MADE I.S.R. SYSTEMS.
IN LIGHT OF THIS,
THERE ARE SOME THINGS
I MUST DISCUSS WITH MS.
HEKMATYAR. THIS CANNOT WAIT.
SINCERE APOLOGIES,
BUT I MUST TAKE MY LEAVE.
- THIS IS IT. HEKMATYAR'S
LAUNCHING HER ATTACK.
- ( yawns ) DONE AT LAST.
DAMN, MY SHOULDERS HURT.
HAULIN' ALL THOSE CONTRACTS
TO KOKO'S CONNECTIONS
WAS TOUGHER WORK
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
WHAT IS THAT I'M SMELLING?
GERMAN SAUSAGE.
AND SCHWARZBIER TOO!
YAY.
- RIGHT. GATHER EURO GROUP'S
EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE.
- AMALIA, SPAIN HAS JUST
MADE A PREDATOR PURCHASE.
- SPAIN, AS WELL?
IS THAT NASSOS OF THE E.A.E.?
- I'M IN DEEP SHIT! IT'S THAT
HEKMATYAR WOMAN'S DOING.
I MUST RETURN
TO MY COUNTRY AT ONCE.
- DIRECTOR, WHAT HAPPENED?
- IT'S A T.O.B.
SOMEONE'S BUYING UP
MY COMPANY'S STOCK.
SOME NEW BANK INVESTOR
CALLED EURO HEKMA-I.B.
WHAT THAT WOMAN IS DOING
IS BARELY LEGAL.
- IT'S NOT JUST MY WEB.
SHE'S TRYING
TO TEAR ME DOWN TOO.
SO THIS IS THE FULL MIGHT
OF KOKO HEKMATYAR.
- ( ringing )
- I THOUGHT YOU AND I
COULD MEET FOR A CHAT.
HOW ABOUT NOW, PLEASE?
- Koko: SURE THING.
- I'M SO SORRY FOR DISRUPTING
YOUR EVENING, KOKO.
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO MEET ME
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
- PLEASE, AMALIA,
THINK NOTHING OF IT.
AND FORGIVE ME FOR ASKING,
BUT ARE YOU ARMED?
SHOULD I BE WORRIED
ABOUT SNIPERS?
- NO SNIPERS.
THIS GENTLEMAN HAS A GUN.
POOR MAN HAS DOUBLE DUTY AS MY
CONSULTANT AND MY BODYGUARD.
REALLY, YOU CAN RELAX.
I DIDN'T COME HERE WITH THE
INTENTION OF DOING YOU HARM.
- SHOULD ANYONE SHOW UP
WHO WE DEEM TO BE SUSPICIOUS,
WE WILL TAKE
APPROPRIATE COUNTER MEASURES.
AS SUCH, NO, I CAN'T RELAX.
- KOKO, WITH AN
ATTITUDE LIKE THAT,
YOU'LL GIVE YOURSELF AN ULCER.
- TWO SNIPERS.
BITCH IS FULL OF IT.
- NOT NECESSARILY. SHE REALLY
MIGHT NOT KNOW THEY'RE THERE.
THAT WOULD MAKE SENSE
IF YOU KEEP IN MIND
THE INFORMATION
LEHM PASSED ALONG.
COUNTRY B'S MAN
HIRED SOME ASSASSINS
AFTER HE LEFT ENGLAND.
GUESS HE WASN'T TOO HAPPY
ABOUT WHAT KOKO DID.
JUST LIKE HER TO PISS OFF
SOMEONE WITH A SHORT FUSE.
- SOME PEOPLE CAN'T HANDLE
DISAPPOINTMENT. CAN THEY?
MAN, THESE ANTI-INFRARED SUITS
GET WARM.
IDIOTS ARE WIDE OPEN.
AND THEY HAVEN'T TAKEN THEIR
FINGERS OFF THE TRIGGERS
FOR ONE SECOND.
- OH, SUCK IT UP. IT'S NOT
LIKE WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR DAYS.
- I MUST SAY I REGRET NOT
PAYING CLOSER ATTENTION
WHEN WE FIRST MET.
I MIGHT HAVE NOTICED THAT
SWEET LITTLE FACE
OF YOURS IS JUST A MASK.
- YES, IT IS.
I TAKE IT YOU FINALLY
MANAGED TO SEE THROUGH
ALL MY DIVERSIONS.
I WOULD EXPECT NOTHING LESS
OF A FORMER ACTRESS
SUCH AS YOURSELF.
BUT THAT'S THE EXTENT
OF YOUR STRENGTH.
THE FIRST TIME I SAW YOU,
I KNEW IMMEDIATELY
THAT YOU'D NEVER SET FOOT
ON A BATTLEFIELD.
I'M NOT SAYING
THAT AN ARMS DEALER
HAS TO SPEND ALL HER TIME
IN WAR ZONES.
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW
WHAT IT IS YOU'RE SELLING.
WEAPONS GO TO SOLDIERS, WHO USE
THEM TO KILL OTHER SOLDIERS.
IF YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT LOOKS LIKE,
YOU CAN'T HOPE
TO BE SUCCESSFUL,
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
THE TRUE SUBSTANCE
OF YOUR OWN MERCHANDISE.
- YOU SPEAK AS IF
I AM TOTALLY IGNORANT.
I DO KNOW MY COMPANY
SELLS DANGEROUS THINGS.
- "THE BOSS SHOULD ALWAYS
BE SMILING, NO MATTER WHAT."
ONE OF MY OLD BODYGUARDS
SAID THAT.
"COVER YOUR FACE WITH A MASK
AND WRAP YOUR HEART
IN IRON ARMOR".
THOSE ARE WORDS
MY FATHER LIVES BY.
I REMEMBER THEIR ADVICE BECAUSE
THEY COULDN'T BE MORE RIGHT.
BEING IN THE BUSINESS
OF SELLING DANGEROUS THINGS,
AS YOU CALL THEM,
TENDS TO ROT THE SOUL,
MUCH IN THE SAME WAY
A COTTON SHIRT WILL ROT
RIGHT OFF YOUR BODY
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE JUNGLE.
- I SUPPOSE TWO ARMS DEALERS
CANNOT HOPE TO MEET
WITHOUT CONFLICT.
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT SOMEONE
SO NAIVE SHE ONLY BROUGHT
ONE BODYGUARD SHOULD GET OUT
BEFORE SHE GETS BURNED?
- Koko:
NO, I'M NOT SAYING THAT.
BUT I WOULD LIKE
TO SHARE ONE MORE THING.
- I LOVE IT!
I AM HAVING SO MUCH FUN.
DON'T THINK ME CRAZY, BUT I'VE
BEEN TINGLING WITH EXCITEMENT
SINCE I SAW THE HEAD
OF THE E.A.E.
RUN BACK TO HIS HOME COUNTRY.
HE WAS SO ANGRY,
I WAS CONVINCED
HE WAS GOING TO HAVE A STROKE
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
I DON'T DO WHAT I DO BECAUSE
I'M FIGHTING FOR SOME CAUSE
OR BECAUSE I HAVE
A FAMILY TO SUPPORT.
NO, I DO IT
BECAUSE I LIKE THE RUSH.
IT'S LESS AND LESS
OFTEN THESE DAYS
THAT YOU COME ACROSS
SOMEONE WHO CAN THROW
A REALLY STRONG PUNCH,
LET ALONE ANOTHER WOMAN.
I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME,
HONESTLY.
THIS IS THE KIND OF THING
I LIVE FOR--
FUN CHATS LIKE THIS.
ALL YOUR WORK HAS PAID OFF,
KOKO.
WE ARE PULLING OUT
OF THE U.A.V. SALES CAMPAIGN.
THE EURO GROUP CONCEDES DEFEAT
TO YOU THIS TIME AROUND.
- ( laughs )
IT WAS A TOUGH BATTLE.
- "YESTERDAY'S ENEMY,
TOMORROW'S FRIEND."
THAT IS THE EUROPEAN WAY
OF THINKING.
- ( thinking ) OH JEEZ.
- YOU AGREE WITH ME, DON'T YOU?
ENEMIES TODAY
CAN BECOME FRIENDS TOMORROW.
- NO NEED TO REPEAT IT.
I HEARD YOU THE FIRST TIME.
NOW, WHY DID YOU
WANT TO MEET ME?
- ABOUT E.A.E.'S STOCK.
CAN YOU PLEASE DO SOMETHING?
AS A FRIEND?
- WHAT A SURPRISE.
COME NOW, SURELY YOU KNOW
THAT'S NOT THE WAY THIS WORKS.
LET'S REFER BACK TO THAT
DISCUSSION WE HAD A MINUTE AGO.
I AM WELL AWARE
OF HOW EUROPEANS DO THINGS.
BUT I THINK IT
MAY BE TIME FOR YOU
TO RECONSIDER YOUR METHODS.
WE NEED TO DON OUR MASKS
AND STRIKE OUT AT OUR
MUTUAL ENEMIES. THAT'S RIGHT.
THE RECENTLY PRIVATIZED
NATIONAL DEFENSE COMPANIES.
AS WE CAN SEE FROM THE SITUATION
WE JUST FOUND OURSELVES IN,
THEY WILL ONLY SERVE
TO HOLD THE WHOLE GROUP BACK.
THEY THINK OF THEMSELVES
AS UNSINKABLE WARSHIPS,
AND THAT KIND OF CONFIDENCE
DOESN'T VANISH OVERNIGHT.
INVERSELY, THAT WILL--
- Amalia: WOULD YOU CONSIDER
SELLING IT BACK AT 2.5%
OF YOUR T.O.B. PURCHASE PRICE?
- WERE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
THE BEST I CAN OFFER IS 10%.
- 5%.
- ( thinking ) THIS IS INSANE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THESE WOMEN.
THEY'RE CASUALLY DECIDING
THE FATE OF THE ENTIRE E.A.E.
IN SOME FILTHY BACK ALLEY.
( aloud )
SNIPER ONE, SNIPER TWO,
TAKE POSITION AND PREPARE
TO FIRE. DO YOU COPY?
- ROGER.
- KOKO.
- YOU ARE CLEAR TO FIRE.
EXCELLENT SHOOTING, LUTZ.
- ( Wilee laughs ) THEY DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHAT HIT 'EM.
BADASS.
YOU REALLY ARE GOOD, LUTZ.
- THE 270 METERS
ACROSS THE RIVER ISN'T THAT FAR.
EVEN LEHM
COULD HAVE GOTTEN IT DONE.
- SORRY TO STARTLE YOU.
WE HAD SOME TROUBLEMAKERS
TO DEAL WITH.
BUT WE DIDN'T KILL THEM.
I AM WILLING TO SELL, BUT ONLY
IF IT'S DIRECTLY TO YOU.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
HOW DOES 5% SOUND?
- THAT SOUNDS MORE THAN FAIR,
KOKO.
- I THOUGHT IT MIGHT.
SEE YOU AT THE EMBASSY TOMORROW.
- Valmet: I DON'T GET IT.
WHY WERE YOU SO SOFT
ON THAT WOMAN?  UGH!
- YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE SHE SAID
IT WAS FUN TALKING TO ME.
- THEN I MUST BE HAVING
A MILLION TIMES MORE FUN
THAN SHE EVER WILL!
- VALMET, I THINK IT'S SAFER
IF YOU WATCH THE ROAD.
MAN,
TOROHOVSKY WAS A REAL HANDFUL.
RATHER NOT BUTT HEADS
WITH HER AGAIN IF I CAN HELP IT.
BUT PEOPLE LIKE THAT ALWAYS SEEM
TO REAPPEAR SOMEHOW.
THEY COME OUT OF THE WOODWORK
WHEN YOU LEAST EXPECT IT.
CONSIDERING HOW BIG
THIS PLANET IS,
IT'S A SMALL FREAKIN' WORLD.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪