- Koko: MOVE! MOVE!
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE!
ENEMY SIGHTED! PREPARE
FOR COMBAT IMMEDIATELY.
DO YOU COPY ME?
- YEAH, I COPY.
- THEY'VE GOT SHARP EYES.
I DON'T WANT THEM CATCHING ON
TILL THEY'RE RIGHT
WHERE WE WANT 'EM.
NO WAY THIS IS THE ONLY BOAT
THEY'VE GOT.
TOJO, WHAT DO YOU SEE?
- I DO HAVE EYES
ON ANOTHER BOAT APPROACHING.
THREE KILOMETERS
BEHIND HOSTILE ONE.
E.T.A. 60 SECONDS.
- DAMN PIRATES!
YOU JUST MADE THE WORST DECISION
OF YOUR MISERABLE LIVES!
- EVERYONE LIVES
IF YOU DROP ANCHOR NOW!
- KEEP DREAMING, ASSHAT!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Koko: GREAT JOB SPOTTING THOSE
BASTARDS SO QUICKLY, VALMET.
I CAN ALWAYS COUNT ON YOU.
- ( laughs ) FOR YOU, KOKO,
I WOULD LOOK TO THE VERY ENDS
OF THE EARTH--
- GUYS, INCOMING CHOPPER
IN ADDITION TO
HOSTILES ONE AND TWO.
WHAT I'D LIKE TO KNOW
IS WHAT THESE LOWLIFES ARE DOING
WITH SUCH ADVANCED WEAPONRY.
- ( helicopter blades whirring )
- SHE'S RIGHT.
I CAN HEAR THE HELICOPTER NOW.
- Jonah: WE'VE GOT
A SMALL BUT FAST CRAFT
APPROACHING FROM BEHIND.
- ROGER THAT.
WE'RE UP TO THREE HOSTILES NOW.
UGO, PORTSIDE.
HIT HOSTILE THREE WITH AN R.P.G.
JONAH,
STAY DOWN UNTIL IT HITS.
HOSTILES TWO AND THREE
ARE THEIR PRIMARY CRAFT.
THEY'LL LIKELY TRY AND SEND UP
THEIR GOONS TO SEIZE THE SHIP.
BUT WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET THAT HAPPEN, ARE WE?
GOT A VISUAL ON THE COPTER.
IT'S A DENEL AVIATION ORYX,
SO WATCH OUT
FOR THE 80mm ROCKETS.
DON'T LET THAT BASTARD FIRE!
- ( rap song playing )
- Man: WHA--
HOW THE HELL
IS A FREIGHTER FIRING ON US?
HUH?
- HOLY SHIT,
THEY TOOK OUT THE COMMAND BOAT!
- PULL BACK! THEY GOT A GUY
AIMING AT US, PORTSIDE!
R.P.G.!
- ( gun cocks )
- Koko:
WHAT A WASTE OF TIME.
FINISH THEM OFF, LEHM!
- SEE YA, BOYS.
- Jonah:
THE LITTLE SHIT PUNCHED ME.
I SAVED HIS MISERABLE LIFE
AND HE PUNCHED ME.
SO, YEAH.
- ( all laughing )
- ( speaks native language )
- KOKO'S ALWAYS PRETTY MERCILESS
WHEN IT COMES TO
DEALING WITH PIRATES.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I GAVE HIM A LIFE PRESERVER.
HOW IS THAT MERCILESS?
WELL, WE SHOULD MAKE PORT
IN SOUTH AFRICA BEFORE LONG.
- Valmet: AFRICA.
- Scarecrow:
OOH, IS THAT A COHIBA?
OR WAS IT MADE IN CHINA?
ENJOY IT WHILE IT LASTS.
ONCE I'VE GOT MY HOOKS IN YOU,
THAT'LL BE THE END OF FANCY
CIGARS FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
YOU'VE BEEN A BAD BOY.
- NOW, SCARECROW,
SURELY YOU ARE MISTAKEN.
I CAN'T THINK OF ANY REASON
I SHOULD COMMAND YOUR
ATTENTION LIKE THIS.
- REALLY?
LET'S START WITH YOUR PLACE
IN THE DA XINGHAI
TRADING COMPANY.
GUOMING CHEN,
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR.
YOU IMPORT SEEMINGLY LEGIT
MACHINERY TO AFRICA
AND THEN YOU EXPORT
LOADS OF RAW MINERALS.
TO MOST PEOPLE, IT LOOKS LIKE
A SUCCESSFUL,
ABOVE-BOARD BUSINESS.
BUT I AIN'T FOOLED.
YOU SEE, I GOT THIS NOSE
FOR DIRTY MONEY.
AND THE CASH
YOU'VE BEEN HAULING IN
DOESN'T SMELL SO SWEET TO ME.
YOU'RE IN THE ARMS TRADE,
AREN'T YA?
NOT THAT I THINK YOU'D EVER
PERSONALLY GET YOUR HANDS DIRTY,
BUT YOUR LADY FRIEND
OVER THERE
SEEMS TO BE WEARING
EAU DE GUN OIL.
- THAT'S WHAT I LIKE
ABOUT YOU AMERICANS.
YOU PUT SO MUCH TIME AND ENERGY
INTO MAKING A SINGLE JOKE.
- YEAH, SEE,
WHEN I'M DONE WITH YOU,
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE GONNA
FIND ANY OF THIS FUNNY.
IN FACT, WHEN DEALING
WITH US AMERICANS,
I WOULD ADVISE YOU TO--
- ( cell phone rings )
- OH, CRAP, THAT'S ME.
BASICALLY,
DON'T SCREW WITH US.
I'M STEPPING OUT FOR A SEC.
YOU STAY HERE.
I STILL GOT PLENTY OF QUESTIONS
THAT NEED ANSWERS.
ABOUT YOUR CONNECTION
TO KASPER HEKMATYAR, FOR ONE.
NEED PERSUADING?
JUST TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS FINE FELLOW.
ELITE P.M.C. MUSCLE,
WORKIN' FOR ME.
YOU WANT TO DO SO MUCH
AS TAKE A PISS,
YOU'LL HAVE TO GO THROUGH HIM
TO GET THERE.
- ( door opens )
- HEY, AHMAD, WHAT'S UP?
GOT SOME DIRT ON KOKO FOR ME?
IT'S ABOUT DAMN TIME!
- STOP RIGHT THERE.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
THE BATHROOM?
OH!
- Scarecrow: ATLAS, ATLAS.
THAT UKRAINIAN CONTAINER SHIP?
AND IT UNLOADED OVER HALF
ITS CARGO AT THE FIRST PORT?
MISSILES, HUH?
( laughs ) THAT CROOK.
YEAH, KEEP GOING.
- ( grunting )
- ( bones cracking,
man grunting )
- ENOUGH.
DON'T KILL HIM, KAREN.
IT MIGHT CAUSE PROBLEMS.
- ALL RIGHT, SIR.
WHATEVER YOU SAY.
YOUR CANE.
- ( grunts )
UM, YOU'VE GOT
A LITTLE SOMETHING ON YOUR FACE.
- I'LL VISIT THE POWDER ROOM,
GENERAL.
THANK YOU.
- WAIT.
- ( coins dropping )
- THE CAPTAIN OF THE UNIT
ASKED FOR AN ADDITIONAL
CONTAINER'S WORTH?
AND THEY JUST FILLED THE ORDER,
RIGHT THEN AND THERE?
REALLY?
WITHOUT A MONEY TRANSFER?
SO HE JUST HANDED OVER
SOME DIAMONDS?
SERIOUSLY?
DIAMONDS?
( laughs )
- ( door opens )
- HEY, YOU!  GET BACK--
( sighs )
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING DOWN THERE?
I'M NOT PAYING YOU
TO GET YOUR ASS BEAT.
WHAT?  THE WOMAN?
DUDE, THAT IS FUCKING PATHETIC!
- WHERE'S THE UNIT?
- SIR, THEY WERE TOLD TO ARRIVE
IN SOUTH AFRICA AHEAD OF US.
- THE SUCCESS OF THIS OPERATION
HAD BETTER EXCEED
THE INCONVENIENCE
OF THAT MEETING.
FAILURE IS NO OPTION.
- KASPER.
IT WON'T BE MUCH LONGER NOW.
- ( knocking )
- Mokoena: HELLO?  DR. MIAMI?
ARE YOU IN THERE, DOC?
OPEN UP.
( sighs )
- ( Miami humming )
♪ O, TWILIGHT BUTTERFLY ♪
♪ HOW YOU FLY SO HIGH ♪
♪ ABOVE THE RAIN AND CLOUDS
SOARING, YOU AND I... ♪
- THIS WOULD BE A LOT EASIER
IF YOU WOULD ANSWER
WHEN I KNOCK.
- WHAT?
OH, HELLO.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE THERE, MOKOENA.
YOU STARTLED ME.
HANG ON, WHERE'S ALL YOUR GEAR?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE READY
TO LEAVE BY NOW?
- ACTUALLY,
THAT'S THE REASON I'M HERE.
YOU JUST UP
AND ANNOUNCED
THAT YOU WERE HEADING
TO THE MOUNTAINS THIS AFTERNOON.
I CAME BY TO MAKE SURE
YOU WERE NOT SERIOUS.
BUT I WAS WRONG.
YOU CAN'T GO.
YOU HAVE AN APPOINTMENT AT
THE EXPO TOMORROW AT 10:00 A.M.
WITH KOKO HEKMATYAR OF H.C.L.I.
YOU'VE BEEN LOOKING FORWARD
TO THIS FOR A WHOLE YEAR.
- YEAH, KOKO.
THAT LUCKY GIRL.
WE'RE THE SAME AGE, BUT SHE
LOOKS SO MUCH YOUNGER THAN ME.
SORRY, KOKO!
I CAN'T MAKE IT.  OH!
- HUH?
- IT'S BECAUSE OF THE
BUTTERFLIES! THE BUTTERFLIES!
AHH!
- I HAD A FEELING
THAT'S WHAT THIS WAS ABOUT.
- Koko: DR. MIAMI, HUH?
YOU THINK SHE STILL
SPENDS ALL HER TIME
CHASING AFTER BUTTERFLIES?
- PROBABLY SO.
SHE DOES HAVE AN ABNORMAL
OBSESSION WITH THEM.
SHE'S AN OFFICER
IN SOME WORLDWIDE
BUTTERFLY GROUP, APPARENTLY.
THAT'S WHO WE'RE
MEETING TOMORROW--
PROFESSOR MINAMI AMADA,
A.K.A. DR. MIAMI.
SHE'S CURRENTLY IN SOUTH AFRICA
WORKING WITH A
GERMAN TOY FACTORY.
BUT SHE SPECIALIZES IN ROBOTICS,
AND THE STUFF SHE WORKS ON
PRETTY MUCH ALWAYS
GETS CONVERTED FOR MILITARY USE.
- IT DOESN'T BOTHER ME
IF PEOPLE WANT
TO TAKE MY RESEARCH AND USE IT
TO MAKE WEAPONS TO
KILL OTHER PEOPLE.
THAT'S JUST FINE.
I'M A LOT MORE CONCERNED
ABOUT THE BUTTERFLIES'
CONTINUED SURVIVAL.
THEY'RE THE ONES IN DANGER.
HOW MANY BILLIONS OF HUMANS
ARE THERE IN THE WORLD?
TOO MANY.
WE'RE OVER-POPULATED.
- THE MOUNTAIN
YOU'RE THINKING OF
IS COVERED IN SNOW
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
- DON'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT, MOKO!
SEE, I HAVE
EVERYTHING WE NEED.
A G.P.S. UNIT AND THIS THESIS
BY PROFESSOR JAMES,
WORLD-RENOWNED
BUTTERFLY EXPERT!
PROFESSOR JAMES
WILL SHOW THE WAY.
- WHO?
- WE'RE GONNA TRACK DOWN
A RARE BUTTERFLY!
BE READY IN FIVE.
- THIS IS A BAD IDEA, DOC.
- ( laughs )
EVERY MOMENT WE SPEND HERE
IS ONE STOLEN
FROM THE FIGHT TO
SAVE THE BUTTERFLIES!
- CALM DOWN.
- FOUR MINUTES NOW, MOKO!
HURRY.
- WE REALLY SHOULDN'T
BE DOING THIS!
- Valmet: 96, 97,
98, 99.
AFRICA, AFRICA,
AFRICA,
AFRICA.
AFRICA, AFRICA,
AFRICA, AFRICA, AFRICA.
I LOST COUNT SOMEWHERE.
LET ME THINK.
WHERE WAS I?
GOOD MORNING, JONAH.
WHAT'RE YOU UP TO?
- MORNIN'.
NOT A LOT.
- HERE--
A RUBBER PRACTICE KNIFE.
YOU WANT TO JOIN ME
FOR SOME EXERCISES?
BIG SWINGS LEAVE YOU OPEN.
TRY FOR SEVERAL STRIKES,
EVEN IF
THEY'RE JUST SHALLOW ONES.
STAY LOW TO THE EARTH.
IF YOU JUMP, YOU'RE FUCKED.
ONCE YOU'RE IN THE AIR,
I GET TO DICTATE THE FIGHT.
ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
LET'S HIT THE SHOWERS.
- ( Koko groaning )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I'M NOT SURE.
IT'S NOT QUITE TIME
FOR OUR APPOINTMENT.
BUT I'VE GOT THIS
SNEAKING SUSPICION
SHE'S NOT GOING TO SHOW.
- FIVE BUCKS SAYS SHE DOESN'T.
- ( car approaches )
- Malin: MS. HEKMATYAR, HELLO!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I'M TERRIBLY SORRY.
- HMM. HEY, MALIN.
IT'S BEEN AWHILE, HUH?
- IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
I CAME TO GIVE YOU
A MESSAGE FROM DR. MIAMI--
- NO, STOP.
THE VERY FACT THAT YOU'RE
HERE IS MESSAGE ENOUGH.
THE GOOD DOCTOR
RAN OFF SOMEWHERE AGAIN.
DIDN'T SHE?
- THAT'S IT EXACTLY.
I AM TRULY VERY SORRY!
- THERE'S NO NEED
FOR YOU TO APOLOGIZE.
- ( laughs )
- ALSO THERE'S
AN UNRELATED MATTER TO DISCUSS.
- A MYSTERIOUS CHINESE MAN?
- YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
AN OLDER MAN WITH A CANE
AND HIS YOUNG FEMALE ASSISTANT.
THEY PAID FREQUENT VISITS
TO THE DOCTOR.
THE ASSISTANT HAD A COLD,
PIERCING GAZE.
BUT ASIDE FROM THAT,
SHE WAS REALLY RATHER BEAUTIFUL.
THEY'VE BEEN TAKING DR. MIAMI
OUT TO EAT AT PORT ELIZABETH,
AND SHE NEVER
GETS HOME UNTIL LATE.
"THE FRIED RICE WAS AMAZING,"
IS ALL SHE EVER SAYS.
THE DOCTOR CAN BE VERY NAIVE.
SHE WON'T ANSWER ME WHEN I ASK
WHAT THE MAN WAS LIKE.
BOTH SHE AND MOKOENA REFUSE
TO SAY A WORD ON THE SUBJECT.
I THINK SHE'S DOING HER BEST
NOT TO ALARM THE COMPANY,
BUT HONESTLY,
I'M QUITE WORRIED ABOUT HER.
OH, AND IN THE MIDDLE
OF ALL THIS,
SHE APPARENTLY WENT OFF
BUTTERFLY HUNTING.
SHE E-MAILED ME
THE G.P.S. COORDINATES EARLIER.
- ( laughs )
ALL RIGHT, JONAH,
YOU GET ONE GUESS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THIS GATHERING IS?
- A WEAPONS EXPO.
- EXACTLY.
- IS EVERYTHING THEY'RE
SHOWING HERE NEWLY INVENTED?
- MMM, FOR THE MOST PART, NO.
THERE ARE SOME
LOCAL MUNITIONS MANUFACTURERS,
BUT MAINLY
IT'S WESTERN COMPANIES
BRINGING IN UPGRADE PACKAGES
TO IMPROVE PRE-EXISTING WEAPONS.
THAT'S THE TREND NOW.
BUT IT'S GOING TO
CHANGE BEFORE LONG.
- WELL, IF IT ISN'T
THE INESTIMABLE KOKO HEKMATYAR.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
- I KNOW THAT SMARMY VOICE.
PRESIDENT CURRY OF C.C.A.T.
- AH, IT'S KOKO AND YOUNG JONAH.
- WITH MILDO AND LOU IN TOW,
OF COURSE.
- DID YOU BUY
KERN AND KRAUSS'S NEW TOY?
- WASN'T THAT GOING
FOR 200 MILLION EUROS?
- WE CAN'T MAKE A MOVE
WITH THE INFESTATION--
- SO NICE TO SEE YOU AS ALWAYS,
PRESIDENT CURRY.
HOW'S THE EXPO FOR YOU
THIS YEAR?
- A COMPLETE AND UTTER WASTE
OF MY TIME.
I'M GOING TO PULL OUT
OF EAST AND SOUTH AFRICA
FOR THE FORESEEABLE FUTURE.
- OH?
- IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
MISS HEKMATYAR,
I MUST BE GOING.
- GOOD AFTERNOON,
MS. HEKMATYAR.
YOU ARE KOKO HEKMATYAR?
I AM GUO MING CHEN OF THE
DA SHINGHAI TRADING COMPANY
OF HONG KONG.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
- OH NO, MR. CHEN,
THE PLEASURE IS ALL MINE.
- I HATE TO IMPOSE UPON YOU,
BUT COULD YOU MAKE ROOM
IN YOUR SCHEDULE
TO MEET WITH ME TONIGHT?
AS YOU CAN SEE,
I HAVE SOME DIFFICULTY STANDING
FOR LONG PERIODS OF TIME.
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED,
PERHAPS I CAN TAKE YOU
OUT TO DINNER SOMEWHERE?
- MAKE IT HIGH-END CHINESE,
AND YOU'VE GOT A DEAL!
- ( laughs )
YOU'RE A FASCINATING
YOUNG LADY.
I MUST RETIRE NOW.
I LOOK FORWARD TO DINNER.
- LEHM?
- YOU RANG?
- A CHINESE GENTLEMAN INVITED ME
OUT TO DINNER THIS EVENING.
- NICE.
SO I ASSUME YOU'RE GOING?
- CHECK THIS OUT, AND GO ARMED.
- RIGHT.  I'M ON IT.
- PASS ALONG TO KAREN THAT THE
WOMAN'S UNIT IS ON THE MOVE.
- YES, SIR.
- Lutz:
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU SAY.
EIGHT PEOPLE IN ONE CAR?
IT'S TOO MUCH.
- YOU'LL WANT TO WRAP THAT GUN
UP IN WHITE TAPE FOR CAMOUFLAGE.
DID EVERYONE
GET A LOOK AT THE PHOTO?
OUR MISSION IS TO SECURE
THIS WOMAN, DR. MIAMI.
AND IF ANYBODY OUT HERE
TRIES TO GET IN OUR WAY, WELL--
--WE ELIMINATE 'EM, BOYS.
- I REALLY DON'T THINK
WE'RE GOING TO SEE
ANY BUTTERFLIES THIS TRIP.
DOCTOR?
- PATIENCE, MOKO.
WE HAVE TO KEEP GOING.
THEY'RE DOWN THERE.
IT'S A VERITABLE
BUTTERFLY PARADISE.
AND YOU-- YOU WOULD TAKE A GUN
AMONGST THEM?
- I HAVE TO PROTECT YOU.
WHO KNOWS
WHAT WE MIGHT FIND UP HERE?
- RIDICULOUS.
- COME ON.
I'D LIKE TO FIND THIS DOCTOR
BEFORE MY BALLS FREEZE OFF.
- LIEUTENANT?
- ESTIMATED DISTANCE?
- ABOUT 200 METERS.
THEY'RE CARRYING
SUBMACHINE GUNS,
ASSAULT RIFLES
AND SNIPER RIFLES.
DR. MINAMI HAS NOT YET
REACHED POINT PARADISE.
SHE'S MOVING AT A NORMAL PACE.
- KEEP THIS DISTANCE,
BUT AHEAD OF THEM.  MOVE.
I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE DAMN DOCTOR.
IT'S HEKMATYAR'S PEOPLE
I WANT.
I'LL SLAUGHTER THEM ALL
AND AVENGE THE MEN
WHOSE LIVES KASPER STOLE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, JONAH?
ANY HOSTILES OUT THERE?
- YEAH, EIGHT OF 'EM.
BUT YOU SHOULDN'T
BE ASKING ME THAT.
IT'S BETTER PRACTICE IF WE EACH
FIGURE IT OUT ON OUR OWN.
- ( laughs )
HE GOT YOU THERE.
YOU KNOW, LUTZ,
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO TRAIN
IN THE MOUNTAINS WITH JONAH
FOR A MONTH OR SO.
- YOU STAY OUT OF IT.
- KEEP YOUR VOICES
DOWN, CHILDREN.
THIS ISN'T A FIELD TRIP.
- Jonah: TOJO.
CAN YOU REMIND ME THE NAME
OF THAT DOCTOR LADY AGAIN?
- OH, UH, MIAMI,
LIKE THAT CITY IN AMERICA.
- HUH?
- MIAMI!
- SCATTER.
- DOCTOR!
DOCTOR!
DOCTOR MIAMI!
- IT'S JUST A BLUFF.
STAY DOWN.
- DOCTOR.
HEY, DOCTOR.
- DAMN IT!
THEY FIGURED OUT WHERE WE ARE.
- NO!  HE'S JUST SHOOTING BLIND,
HOPING TO HIT US.
- JONAH, CAN YOU SEE THE ENEMY?
WHERE ARE THEY?
- NO IDEA. I'M JUST SHOOTING
TILL I FIND 'EM.
- DAMN.
- IDIOT.
- WELL, LOOK AT THAT.
THE ARMY ANTS ARE COMING OUT.
I CAN'T SAY THAT'S THE METHOD
I WOULD HAVE GONE WITH.
BUT I'VE GOTTA
GIVE THE KID CREDIT
FOR SCREWING UP WHATEVER AMBUSH
THEY PLANNED.
- Karen:
OUR PLAN IS RUINED NOW.
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU.
YOU SCREWED UP
DURING THE KASPER INCIDENT TOO.
APOLOGIZE FROM HELL.
- VALMET?
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪