- YOU GAVE THE GO FOR NIGHT NINE
WITHOUT AUTHORIZATION.
- SIR, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I FILED ALL THE PAPERWORK.
- IT SEEMS THAT PAPERWORK
HASN'T MADE ITS WAY
THROUGH PROPER CHANNELS.
- SORRY, SIR, I'LL TRY
TO FIND OUT WHAT WENT WRONG.
- ( hangs up)
- ( beeps )
- MAKES MY CHEST HURT,
HAVING TO HAMSTRING
SUCH A PROMISING
YOUNG OPERATIVE.
- Black: YOU SHOULD
GET THAT LOOKED AT.
- YEAH, WELL,
DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH TIME
ME YELLING AT HIM GETS YA,
BUT I HOPE IT'S ENOUGH TO
FULFILL MY END OF OUR DEAL.
- IT IS.
NICELY DONE, WOODY.
AND THANKS FOR TIPPING ME OFF
TO THE SEALS' ATTACK PLAN
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- I CAN'T PULL THIS CRAP AGAIN.
PLAME WILL QUESTION
MY COMPETENCE.
I DON'T KNOW WHOSE
ASS YOU'RE COVERING,
YOURS OR SOMEONE ELSE'S,
BUT ARE YOU SURE
THIS IS REALLY WORTH IT?
OH, WHATEVER.
KNOWING YOU, IT'LL WORK OUT.
STILL, I WANT ASSURANCES
YOU'LL KEEP YOUR END.
- THAT CUTE 20-YEAR-OLD REDHEAD
YOU'VE GOT ON THE SIDE?
NO ONE'LL EVER KNOW
ABOUT YOU TWO.
- ( chuckles )
THAT'S ALL I NEEDED TO HEAR.
- ( rain pattering )
- ( cloth flapping )
- OPERATION IS A GO.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THIS IS PET SHOP!
LOOKS LIKE WE'VE HAD A BREAK-IN!
I REPEAT,
THE MERCHANDISE IS STOLEN!
- HEY, STOP!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SERIOUSLY,
YOU CAN'T JUST KIDNAP PEOPLE.
PUT ME BACK!
THIS WON'T END WELL...
FOR ME
OR FOR WHOEVER YOU ARE!
- KEEP QUIET, DOCTOR.
- Man: AT 1900 HOURS,
EIGHT UNIDENTIFIED MERCENARIES
ABDUCTED THE DETAINEE
"CHATTY RABBIT'S FOOT."
THE MARINE DETACHMENT
PROVIDING TRANSPORT
SUFFERED ZERO CASUALTIES.
BUT THE MERCENARIES ARE
CURRENTLY HEADING DUE WEST
TOWARD THE CUBAN BORDER.
NIGHT NINE IS AWAITING
A GO ORDER.
- ( beeps )
- Woody: YOU HAVE APPROVAL
ON THE NIGHT NINE OP.
- EXCELLENT, SIR.
THANK YOU.
- Soldier: GREAT. NOT ONLY IS
NO ONE COMING TO SAVE US,
IT'S RAINING.
- Soldier #2: WHY'D THEY HAVE TO
MAKE THESE KNOTS SO TIGHT?
- Soldier #3:WE'RE SITTING DUCKS
IF THE CUBANS JUMP THE FENCE.
- HEY, IT SNAPPED.
THE HELL?
- ( buzzes )
- HUH?
( clicking )
- Lehm: DAMN IT. THINK WE'VE GOT
SOME MARINES ON OUR TAILS.
THIS COULD GET UGLY.
- Jonah: THEN WE'D BETTER HURRY.
- Lutz: WHAT'S UP?
SOMETHING WRONG?
- Valmet: WE GOTTA MOVE.
- HEY! ( grunts )
- GREAT, THEY'VE SENT OUT
A STRIKE TEAM AFTER US.
( laughs )
SO ARROGANT.
LEHM AND THE OTHERS WON'T BE
TAKEN OUT  BY THE LIKES OF YOU,
ESPECIALLY NOT WITH ME
ON THEIR SIDE.
HEY, IT'S ME.
YEAH, IT'S SHOWTIME.
- Plame: DRAGGING CHATTY
RABBIT'S FOOT THROUGH THE JUNGLE
IS SLOWING THEM DOWN.
WE'RE CLOSING IN.
PREPARE TO ENGAGE.
JUST REMEMBER, THE CUBAN
REVOLUTIONARY ARMED FORCES
HAVE SEVERAL
COMBAT BRIGADES IN THE AREA.
BE WARY OF THEIR DISTANCE.
IF AT ALL POSSIBLE,
KEEP RABBIT'S FOOT ALIVE.
HOWEVER, YOU'RE CLEAR
TO SANCTION THE REST.
NIGHT NINE,
YOU ARE A GO.
- ROCKET.
- ( rock music playing )
- THEY'RE HERE!
- ( cocks )
- Lehm:
HOSTILES! SPLIT UP!
DON'T LET 'EM FLANK YOU!
- ( whimpering )
( screams ) SEE? I TOLD YOU
THIS WOULDN'T END WELL!
- Valmet:
WOULD YOU PLEASE KEEP IT DOWN?
- ALL THIS WOOD AND RAIN IS
A DOING A NUMBER ON MY AIM.
AND THESE BASTARDS
ARE STRONG AND FAST.
WHO ARE THEY?
SHIT.  GOTTA MOVE.
( grunts )
ARE YOU SHITTING ME?
MY ASS AGAIN?!  IT'S LIKE
THE DAMNED THING'S CURSED!
- LUTZ!
- Woman: PILOT, LOOP BACK
OVER THE BATTLEFIELD.
- COPY THAT, SEARCH.
HAVE VISUAL ON TARGET.
- THEY ARE RESILIENT.
THESE TWO ON THE LEFT FLANK
ARE PROBABLY SNIPERS.
HAVE THE NORTHERNMOST UNIT
BREAK OFF AND INTERCEPT.
- THE PREDATOR'S PICKED UP
SOMETHING FAINT ON RADAR.
- EAT THIS.
SPIKE-L.R. MISSILES,
DO YOUR THING.
- WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
YES!
( laughs )
I'VE BLINDED
YOU BITCHES WITH SCIENCE!
OH, AND I AM JUST
GETTING STARTED.
- SOMEONE'S JAMMING
OUR G.P.S.
WE'LL HAVE TO CONNECT
TO THE TACTICAL DATA LINK
TO GET REAL-TIME INTEL
ON OUR LOCATION.
- Jonah: LUTZ.
- JONAH.
I'M FINE,
I CAN STILL RUN.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO COME OVER HERE.
BUT YOU'RE LOSING
A LOT OF BLOOD.
- I JUST GOT GRAZED.
IT LOOKS WORSE THAN IT IS.
DON'T WORRY.
BESIDES, IT'S MORT IMPORTANT
THAT WE GET MOVING.
( both grunting )
( yelps )
- OH CRAP, WE'VE BEEN SEPARATED
FROM THE OTHERS.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE MAP
KOKO MADE US LEARN?
- YEAH, I THINK
WE'RE RIGHT ON THE BORDER.
CRAP, WE'RE STUCK.
WE'RE IN A MINEFIELD!
- Plame:
G.P.S. JAMMER, HUH?
I EXPECTED A FIREFIGHT,
NOT ELECTRONIC WARFARE.
- Woman: NIGHT NINE IS CONNECTED
TO THE TACTICAL DATA LINK.
- WE'RE TOO RELIANT
ON DIGITAL INTEL.
WE NEED EYES ON.
FIND 'EM BEFORE THEY GET AWAY.
AIR SUPPORT?
- WITH THE BAD WEATHER,
MQ-9 REAPER CAN'T
GET AIRBORNE SAFELY, SIR.
- PREDATOR CRASH...
IS CONFIRMED.
THANKFULLY
THE WIND AND FLIGHT PATH
RESULTED IN IT SCATTERING
ON OUR SIDE OF THE CUBAN BORDER.
- FINALLY, SOME GOOD NEWS.
IF IT CRASHED TWO KLICKS
IN THE OTHER DIRECTION,
I'D BE OUT OF A JOB.
- THESE GUYS AREN'T
BACKING DOWN.
I CAN SO PICTURE
THE AGENT BEHIND THIS--
SOME UPTIGHT FOUR-EYED
DOUCHEBAG
TRYING TO MAKE A
NAME FOR HIMSELF.
- Miami on phone:
WELL, YOU PREDICTED RIGHT,
THE ENEMY UNIT'S COMPLETED
THEIR CONNECTION
WITH THE TACTICAL DATA LINK.
BABS SAYS
THEY'RE USING PORTAL 16.
SHE'S UPLOADING YOU
THEIR SPECIFIC IP ADDRESS.
I HATE TO SEE THE FUN END,
BUT I THINK YOU'VE
WON THIS BATTLE.
- NO, IT'S NOT DONE
UNTIL THE WHOLE TEAM'S
BACK IN ONE PIECE.
- YOU ARE GOING SOFT.
- MINAMI, GIVE THEM JUST
A LITTLE TASTE OF JORMUNGAND.
- SOUNDS FUN.
- ( rock music playing )
- ( distant gunfire )
- JONAH, I JUST HEARD
FROM THE LITTLE LADY.
SHE WANTS US TO HOLD TIGHT.
- THOSE GUYS IN GREEN
ARE TOUGHER THAN
MOST OF OUR OPPONENTS.
- WOW.
YOU'VE GOT GOOD EYES
IF YOU CAN TELL
THEY'RE WEARING GREEN.
- LEHM AND THE OTHERS ARE GONNA
HAVE A HARD TIME WITHOUT US.
BESIDES--
- EVEN IF WE STAY HERE,
KOKO'S NOT COMING, RIGHT?
BEFORE THE OP, I DID SAY SOME
PRETTY CRITICAL STUFF TO HER.
- YEAH, THAT.
- WELL, THE LITTLE LADY'S
NOT THE TYPE OF PERSON
TO CHANGE HOW SHE DOES THINGS
JUST 'CAUSE I SPEAK UP.
SHE EXPECTS ME
TO OBEY EVERY ORDER,
BUT WE CAN'T
EXACTLY SIT HERE EITHER.
HOW DO WE GET BACK UP THERE?
- WILLPOWER.
- ACCORDING TO KOKO,
WE'VE ALREADY WON
THE BATTLE IN THE AIR.
DAMN! THESE GUYS
ON THE GROUND ARE TOUGH.
MIGHT EVEN BE
DEADLIER THAN US!
KEEP WHINING,
TOJO AND THEY WILL BE.
- Leila: PLEASE!
EVERYONE STOP SHOOTING!
IF YOU DON'T HIT ME, YOU'RE
GOING TO SCARE ME TO DEATH!
- DAMN.  THESE GUYS ARE
MAKING ME LOOK BAD.
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN A CLEAN HIT
ON ONE OF 'EM YET.
- YOU TOO, LEHM?
- WHY AREN'T THEY FLANKING THEM?
- Woman: ENEMY SNIPERS ARE
HOLDING THE SEAL'S BACK.
- IT'S THOSE TWO
WHO GOT SPLIT OFF.
- ALL RIGHT, NOW IT'S GETTING
FUN. I LOVE AN AMBUSH.
- GUYS, THAT COVER-FIRE'S
FROM LUTZ AND JONAH!
DIDN'T THE BOSS
TELL THEM SO SIT TIGHT?
- Koko: IT'S OKAY, LEHM.
YOU GUYS JUST KEEP RUNNING.
- ( chuckles )
ALL RIGHT, I TRUST YOU, KOKO.
- Wilee:
THEY STOPPED SHOOTING!
- WHAT THE HELL? I THOUGHT
THEY WERE RIGHT ON US.
- Man:
HOTEL 5! HOTEL 5!
THIS IS ROOM 3.
KEEP YOUR DISTANCE
FROM THAT BORDER.
- ( grunts )
- JONAH!
- ( gasps )
- Man: CEASE FIRE!
REPEAT, ALL UNITS CEASE FIRE!
WE ENDED UP
AT THE BORDER SOMEHOW.
- JESUS!
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
HOW COULD ALL
OF OUR MAPS BE WRONG?
( grumbles )
- AWAITING ORDERS, SIR.
- Plame:
NIGHT NINE, PULL BACK.
( breathing hard )
KOKO HEKTMATYAR.
- HUH.  THAT'S WEIRD.
THEY'RE ALL GONE.
- YEAH, LIKE THEY WERE
NEVER HERE.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I NEVER SHOULD'VE DOUBTED
THE LITTLE LADY
GETTING US OUT OF THIS JAM.
- YOU REALLY THINK SHE DID THIS?
- Koko:
ATTENTION, DISOBEDIENT DUO,
GO TO RENDEZVOUS POINT ALPHA.
AND MAKE SURE YOU STICK
TO THE MAPS I MADE YOU MEMORIZE.
( chuckles )
- Valmet:
THE STORM'S FINALLY PASSED,
MR. I-LIKE-TO-DISOBEY-
DIRECT-ORDERS.
- YUP.
- AND WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THIS WARM TROPICAL BREEZE
THAT'S REPLACED IT,
MR. DISRESPECTFUL JERK?
- FINE, I GET IT.  I'M SORRY
I DISOBEYED KOKO'S ORDERS.
LITTLE LADY ALREADY
CHEWED ME OUT TOO, YOU KNOW.
- I FINALLY HAVE AN ANSWER
FOR THAT QUESTION
YOU ASKED THE OTHER DAY,
THE WHOLE
"IS KOKO BECOMING TOO AGGRESSIVE
AND DO WE KEEP FOLLOWING HER?"
BUT ARE YOU SURE
YOU STILL WANNA HEAR IT?
I MEAN, AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED TODAY.
- ( chuckles )
NOT AT ALL.
LITTLE LADY MAY BE
A BIT OFF-KILTER,
BUT SHE WON'T ABANDON
HER FRIENDS.
- BEST BOSS EVER.
- THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
- Lutz's voice:
LEHM SAID THOSE GUYS TODAY
WERE A SECRET SQUAD
OF THE NAVY SEALS' BEST.
NO WAY THEY'D MISREAD THE LAY
OF THE LAND LIKE THAT...
UNLESS...
KOKO REALLY IS OPERATING
ON A WHOLE OTHER LEVEL
FROM EVERYONE ELSE.
- MAN, I'M ALL SCRAPED UP.
( yelps )
- ( blabbers )
- KOKO?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE!
- YOU CAN'T YELL AT ME!
YOU'RE THE DISOBEDIENT ONE!
- NOW TAKE
YOUR TICKLE PUNISHMENT!
- THOSE GUYS TODAY
WERE PRETTY HARDCORE.
DID YOU DO SOMETHING
TO GET 'EM TO PULL BACK
LIKE THAT?
- IT'S A SECRET.
JUST KIDDING.
ONCE WE GET TO PORT,
I PROMISE I'LL ANSWER
ANY QUESTIONS YOU HAVE.
IF YOU ANSWER
MY QUESTION FIRST.
IT'S SOMETHING I'VE WANTED
TO ASK YOU FOR A WHILE NOW.
YOU ONCE SAID THE WORLD MIGHT
HATE YOU, BUT YOU STILL LOVE IT.
AFTER ALL THE MISSIONS
WE'VE BEEN ON TOGETHER,
DO YOU STILL FEEL THAT WAY?
- YEAH, ACTUALLY, I DO.
I MIGHT EVEN LOVE IT EVEN MORE.
I'VE SEEN SO MANY
PEOPLE AND PLACES,
BUT I WANNA SEE THE REST.
AND THE LONGER
I TRAVEL WITH YOU,
THE MORE I FEEL THAT WAY.
BUT SEEING THE WORLD
THROUGH A RIFLE SCOPE
ISN'T REALLY SEEING
THE WORLD, IS IT?
I KNOW THAT WAR IS WHAT WE DO
AND I'M A SOLDIER ON THE GROUND,
ONE WHO'S SUPPOSED
TO DO WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO KEEP YOU SAFE AND ALIVE.
BUT I DON'T WANNA SEE
ANY MORE FRIENDS DIE.
LIKE R.
- OH JONAH!
YOU'RE LIKE A LOYAL
LITTLE PUPPY DOG.
YOU'RE EXACTLY
WHAT I NEED IN A BODYGUARD.
AND I'LL NEVER STOP
PROTECTING YOU GUYS EITHER.
YOU KEPT YOUR END
OF THE BARGAIN.
SO I'LL TELL YOU EVERYTHING
AT PORT LIKE I SAID--
NOT ONLY HOW I GOT
THOSE NAVY SEALS TO RETREAT
BUT ALSO THE TRUE NATURE
OF JORMUNGAND.
OH JONAH, IT'S GONNA BLOW
YOUR MIND WHEN YOU HEAR IT.
- ( jet approaching )
- Black: WE'VE HAD SOME ISSUES
WITH THE LITTLE LADY RECENTLY
THAT HAVE KEPT ME
AT THE OFFICE,
BUT SINCE YOU'RE IN TOWN,
SCARECROW,
I FIGURED I'D BETTER
COME SEE YOU IN PERSON.
- I'LL TAKE THAT
AS A COMPLIMENT.
WHAT SHE DO NOW?
HACK YOU GUYS
WITH A QUANTUM COMPUTER
OR SOMETHING OUT
OF A SCI-FI MOVIE?
- WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU KNEW ABOUT THAT?
- I DIDN'T KNOW, BUT I FIGURE
IF I HAD HER KIND OF MONEY,
I'D TRY AND CREATE
A DEVICE THAT
WOULD MAKE MYSELF INVINCIBLE
AND EVERYONE ELSE OBSOLETE.
- ( humphs )
SO THOSE ARE THE POWER-MAD
FANTASIES OF YOUR GENERATION.
NOTHING ABOUT
THAT COMPUTER'S CONFIRMED.
WE DON'T KNOW
WHETHER SHE USED IT ON US
OR IF IT EVEN EXISTS.
RIGHT NOW MY TEAM'S
LOOKING AT ALL POSSIBILITIES
BEFORE FILING
OUR OFFICIAL REPORT.
WHAT WE DO KNOW IS
SHE SENT A SEAL TEAM
IN ACCURATE G.P.S. INFO.
AND USED THAT OPENING
TO ABSCOND WITH A DETAINEE
SHE STOLE FROM GITMO.
BUT WHAT'S REALLY
THROWING US IS THERE'S NO SIGN
THE DATA LINK WAS HACKED.
THING IS,
THAT'S ALL WE KNOW SO FAR.
WITH HER, IT SEEMS LESS SCI-FI
AND MORE LIKE MAGIC.
- ( laughs )
SHE'S USING MAGIC?
I'M OUT THERE
BUSTING MY HUMP
DOING ACTUAL
INVESTIGATIVE WORK...
WHILE YOU'RE THROWING UP
YOUR HANDS, SAYING,
"WE CAN'T POSSIBLY STOP HER
BECAUSE MAGIC!"
- HOW DO YOU THINK I FEEL?
MY WHOLE OPERATION
WAS PREMISED ON THE IDEA
I COULD MANIPULATE HER
TO MY OWN ENDS!
NO WAY IN HELL
THAT'S EVER GONNA HAPPEN NOW.
- ( both laughing )
- WOW. DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER SEEN EITHER OF THEM
LAUGH FOR REAL LIKE THAT.
- Leila: WHERE THE FRAK
ARE YOU TAKING ME?!
- CALM DOWN, DR. FAIZA.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY
TO SOUTH AFRICA.
- WHY SOUTH AFRICA?
AND WHO THE HELL ARE YOU PEOPLE?
AND HOW DO YOU KNOW
SO MUCH ABOUT ME?
I'VE HAD IT WITH
ALL THE SPY STUFF AND SHOOTOUTS!
IF YOU PLAN
ON WORKING ME LIKE A SLAVE,
YOU MIGHT AS WELL SHOOT ME NOW,
'CAUSE I WON'T DO IT!
- NOW I SEE WHERE THE "CHATTY"
PART OF YOUR HANDLE COMES FROM.
I'VE COME TO HATE PEOPLE
WITH BIG MOUTHS LIKE YOURS.
INFORMATION IS
THE MOST VALUABLE COMMODITY.
ALL THE MONEY IN THE WORLD
CAN'T BUY THE MOST
CLASSIFIED BITS OF INTEL.
SOME PEOPLE SPEND
THEIR WHOLE LIVES
CHASING SECRETS,
AND MANY OF THEM
DIE IN THE PROCESS.
EVEN IF YOU'RE THE BEST HACKER
AND FINDING
GOVERNMENT SECRETS COMES EASY,
THERE'S STILL SOMEONE WILLING
TO DIE TO KEEP THEM COVERED UP.
WHEN YOU TALK, YOU'RE
SHOWING DISRESPECT
FOR THE INFO YOU STEAL.
- BOLD WORDS FROM A KIDNAPPER!
- FORGET SECRETS.
I'M GIVING YOU A NEW TOY.
DR. MINAMI AMADA AND I
DESIGNED THE PLANS,
THEN WE BROUGHT
IN DR. ELENA BABURIN
TO BREATHE LIFE
THIS MASTERPIECE.
- THEN YOU'RE BUILDING A--
- FOR YEARS, MINAMI AND I KEPT
THE PROJECT BETWEEN
JUST THE TWO OF US,
BUT WE NEEDED DR. BABURIN.
AND NOW BECAUSE OF YOUR SMARTS,
MINAMI INSISTS WE NEED YOU, TOO.
( laughs )
FOR ONCE YOU'RE SPEECHLESS.
GUESS MINABI WAS RIGHT
THAT IF I GIVE YOU A PROJECT
THAT TICKLES YOUR GENIUS BRAIN,
YOU'LL QUIT FREAKING OUT
AND COME AROUND
TO OUR WAY OF THINKING.
JUST DON'T GO BLABBING ABOUT
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE, OKAY?
WHO KNOWS? YOU MIGHT SPEND
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
PLAYING WITH THIS NEW TOY.
- ( door opens )
- OH, AND IF YOU DO BLAB,
YOU'RE DEAD.
( whimpers )
AM I GONNA BE SOMEONE'S PRISONER
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE?
SHE WASN'T LYING
ABOUT SOUTH AFRICA.
THAT'S REALLY TABLE MOUNTAIN
ON THE HORIZON.
OH, BRR.
AND IS THE GROUND MOVING?
- FIRST, I WILL TAKE THE SKIES
FROM THE HUMAN RACE!
MILITARY AIRCRAFT,
CIVILIAN PLANES,
SPACE CAPSULES,
ROCKETS, I.C.B.M.s.
ON MY ORDER,
EVERY COUNTRY IN THE WORLD
WILL BECOME NAILED
TO THE GROUND.
HUMANITY WILL LOSE ITS
BEST FORM OF TRANSPORTATION
AND THE SKIES WILL BE THRUST
OVER A HUNDRED YEARS
INTO THE PAST.
- ( gasps )
- Koko: AS YOU KNOW,
H.C.L.I. HAS LAUNCHED
126 SATELLITES.
THIS GLOBAL POSITIONING SYSTEM,
IN CONCERT WITH THE QUANTUM
COMPUTER MINAMI AND I DESIGNED,
WILL LIMIT THE
MOBILITY OF EVERY
TRANSPORTATION SYSTEM ON EARTH--
FIRST IN THE SKY,
THEN AT SEA,
AND THEN FINALLY ON THE LAND.
IT WILL GIVE US
COMPETE CONTROL
OVER WORLDWIDE
DISTRIBUTION NETWORKS.
AND WITH THIS POWER,
THE WORLD WILL KNOW PEACE!
AND THEY WILL
OWE IT ALL TO ME,
AN ARMS DEALER.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF PEOPLE OUT
THERE WHO CLAIM TO WANT PEACE.
YET IRONICALLY,
IT TOOK A WAR PROFITEER LIKE ME
TO TRULY ACHIEVE
A LASTING SOLUTION.
( laughing )
I SWEAR, YOU'D THINK
THE WORLD IS FULL OF IDIOTS!
SEPARATING MILITARY
FROM LOGISTICS,
PERMANENTLY TEARING HUMANS AWAY
FROM MILITARY AFFAIRS--
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS
ALL ABOUT, MY FRIENDS.
THAT IS MY ULTIMATE GOAL!
BUT YOU WILL HOLD
YOUR GUNS TO THE END,
BECOMING THE LAST SOLDIERS
ON EARTH!
AND YOU WILL PROTECT ME.
- ( chuckles )
YOU'VE GOT IT, KOKO.
- HOLD ON A SEC, KOKO.
YOU'RE SAYING THE FUTURE
IS YOU PLAYING GOD?
IT IS SAID THAT GOD
ONCE SENT AN ANGEL
TO SMITE
185,000 ASSYRIAN SOLDIERS.
BUT WHETHER KILLED
BY GOD OR AN ENEMY,
SOLDIERS ARE EXPECTED TO DIE.
IF A BATTLEFIELD SLAUGHTER
IS THE BEST GOD CAN DO,
I WOULD THINK
THAT ME PREVENTING THOSE MEN
FROM BECOMING SOLDIERS
IN THE FIRST PLACE
MAKES ME GREATER THAN GOD.
- ( groans )
- ( hip-hop music playing )
- Jonah: HOW MANY WILL DIE?
- HMM?
- AS A RESULT
OF PROJECT JORMUNGAND?
GOOD QUESTION.
I'LL TEXT MINAMI.
IT'S TRUE,
PEOPLE WILL DIE
WHEN EVERY PLANE IN THE SKY
DROPS ALL AT ONCE,
BUT THAT NUMBER
IS INSIGNIFICANT
NEXT TO THOSE
WHO WOULD OTHERWISE DIE
IN THE FUTURE WARS
WE'LL BE PREVENTING.
OH LOOK,
SHE SENT AN ANSWER.
SHE SAYS THAT RIGHT NOW
THERE ARE 683,822 PEOPLE
IN VARIOUS PLANES
AND SPACECRAFT.
SO ABOUT 700,000.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, JONAH?
YOU IN?
- ( guns cock )
- ( gasps )
- DON'T DO THIS.
NO MATTER YOUR REASONS, KOKO,
YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
- Koko: JONAH.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO ♪
♪ SHE IS--
OH, NO NO NO NO... ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪