- Man: I HAVE DEVOURED
FIVE CONTINENTS.
I HAVE SLURPED
THREE OCEANS DRY.
THE VAST SKY ALONE REMAINS
OUT OF MY LONG REACH.
FOR I AM TRAPPED IN THIS
BODY, WHICH LACKS WINGS,
HANDS, AND FEET.
I AM THE WORLD SERPENT.
I AM JORMUNGAND.
- Jonah: OUR PATH
IS SO OVERRUN WITH WEAPONS
THAT SOMETIMES I WONDER
IF THE WHOLE WORLD
IS MADE UP OF NOTHING
BUT IRON AND GUNPOWDER.
AS I CLENCHED THAT TOOL,
DESIGNED FOR THE SOLE PURPOSE
OF TAKING LIVES,
I HATED THE WEAPON
MORE THAN EVER.
HERE I AM,
TRAVELING WITH AN ARMS DEALER.
AND ALL I SEE
IS A CHANGING WORLD.
- ( theme music playing )
- MOKO!  THEY TURNED
MISTER CHEN'S RESTAURANT
INTO A DUMB,
RUN-OF-THE-MILL SUPERMARKET.
- SURE DID, DOC.
IT'S NOT BAD,
AS FAR AS SUPERMARKETS GO.
REASONABLE PRICES.
NOW THAT YOU MENTION HIM,
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE WE'VE HEARD
THE SLIGHTEST PEEP
FROM MISTER CHEN, HASN'T IT?
- HMM.
MMM?
KAREN?
IS THAT YOU?
YOU ARE MISTER CHEN'S SECRETARY,
RIGHT?
LIEUTENANT KAREN LOW?
- THAT'S "FORMER,"
DOCTOR AMADA.
FORMER LIEUTENANT NOW.
BUT HOW COULD YOU TELL
I WAS MILITARY
WHEN I LOOK THIS WAY?
- IF YOU'VE GOT NOWHERE TO GO,
YOU SHOULD COME WITH ME.
IT'LL BE FANTASTIC!
YOU CAN BE MY SECRETARY
AT MY LAB IN MARSCHEN.
I ALREADY HAVE TWO,
BUT I COULD USE ANOTHER.
WEREN'T YOU IN ALEXANDRIA?
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
YOUR SALARY
IS TOTALLY NEGOTIABLE.
BOY, IT'S CHILLY OUT HERE.
YOU'LL CATCH A COLD
DRESSED LIKE THAT.
OH, WAIT, YOU'RE INJURED.
ARE YOU OKAY?
'CAUSE YOU SURE DON'T LOOK IT.
WE CAN FIX YOU UP AT MY PLACE.
THE BIG GUY'S MOKOENA.
TRY TO GET ALONG.
OH.
YOU'VE ALREADY MET?
THEN YOU CAN
JUST CALL HIM MOKO!
I ALSO HAVE
ANOTHER ASSISTANT NAMED MALIN.
RECENTLY WE'VE HAD PEOPLE
SNOOPING AROUND
WHO REEK OF THE C.I.A.
THAT OR INDUSTRY SPIES.
WOW, KAREN,
HOW DID YOUR EYES GET SO BLUE?
WAIT, YOU'RE HAPA? WHEN WAS
THE LAST TIME YOU BATHED?
YOU CAN SHOWER AT THE OFFICE.
YOU'RE, LIKE,
REALLY STRONG, RIGHT?
I'VE GOT HIGH HOPES!
OH, AND GUESS WHAT?
I JUST MADE THE MOST AWESOME
TOY. IT'LL SELL SO BIG!
- UH, OKAY.
- ( thinking ) LOOKS LIKE DOC'S
TAKEN A REAL LIKING TO HER.
- Karen: GENERAL!
GENERAL!  GENERAL!
- ( bullet zinging )
- Jonah: VALMET?  VALMET?
- I--
I HATE THIS WORLD!
DO YOU HEAR THAT, WORLD?
SCREW YOU!
- Miami: AH, I SEE.
SO THAT'S WHAT WENT DOWN
BETWEEN H.C.L.I.
AND THE DA XINGHAI TRADING
COMPANY. WHAT A MESS.
SO THEN NATURALLY VALMET HAD
TO GET HER REVENGE ON YOU.
AND YOU DIDN'T DARE GO BACK HOME
AFTER ALL OF THAT NONSENSE.
SO BASICALLY, KAREN,
YOU WERE DUMPED IN AFRICA,
ALONE,
TO FEND FOR YOURSELF.
- SOMEHOW I'D FORGOTTEN,
DOCTOR,
HOW DEEPLY YOUR CONNECTIONS
RUN WITH H.C.L.I.
I'M SURE YOU CAN GUESS
WHAT HAPPENED NEXT.
- YEAH.  YOU CAN GET AWAY
WITH A LOT IN AFRICA.
FOR A WHILE, DA XINGHAI
WIELDED A GREAT DEAL OF POWER.
AND YOUR BOSS
WAS DANGEROUS ENOUGH,
AND EYE-PLEASING ENOUGH,
TO STEAL YOUR HEART.
ARE YOU ANGRY AT THE WORLD
'CAUSE YOU LOST
'EM BOTH AT ONCE?
- NO.
I WOULDN'T REALLY SAY THAT.
- THAT FIGURES.
LIKE SOMEONE WHO RUNS AWAY
WITHOUT A FIGHT WOULD BE ABLE
TO FEED HERSELF.
STILL, YOU MUST HAVE FELT
LIKE THE WORLD HAD BEATEN YOU.
BUT SOON,
THAT WORLD IS GOING TO CHANGE.
SO YOU'VE GOT NOTHIN'
TO WORRY ABOUT, OKAY, KAREN?
NOW, SLICE!
NINJA STAR. ( laughs )
THIS IS KUNUTTO,
MY NEW ROBO-NINJA-BEAR.
EVERYBODY'S GONNA WANT ONE.
OKAY, LATERS.
YOU START WORK TOMORROW, COOL?
- GET BACK HERE!
- CORPORATE SPY!
GET HIM. THAT ONE'S C.I.A.!
- RETREAT!
- GET HIS ASS!
- PLEASURE TO MEET YOU--
IT'S TIME FOR THE DOCTOR'S
MEETING WITH THE DEALERS.
WHERE IS SHE?
- I THINK SHE WENT FISHING.
- UH, FISHING?
- I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY!
I'M SO TERRIBLY SORRY.
- MALIN, YOU'RE NOT THE ONE
WHO NEEDS TO APOLOGIZE.
( sighs )
- HEY, KAREN! PACK YOUR BAGS.
LOOK OUT, SOLOMON ISLANDS,
HERE WE COME!
- SO, MINAMI,
WHY WOULD YOU THINK
YOU COULD BRING THIS OUTSIDER
HERE? THAT'S KAREN LOW.
- IT'S ALL GOOD, KOKO.
CHILL.
DON'T BE SO RUDE.
KAREN'S ONE
OF MY SECRETARIES NOW.
I WARNED HER NOT TO START
ANY TROUBLE WHILE SHE'S HERE.
- BAD ENOUGH YOU SHOWED UP
AT THE LAST MINUTE.
HUH?  WHEN DID DOCTOR MIAMI
GET HERE?
- ( both grunting )
- Both: ALL RIGHT, LADIES,
KNOCK IT OFF.
- Both:
SORRY, WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
- AW, NO CATFIGHT?
- ONE MINUTE TO LAUNCH.
- TOO BAD YOUR OLD MAN
IS SUCH A PARTY POOPER.
THIS IS THE FINAL LAUNCH
AND HE'S NEVER SHOWN UP ONCE.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL YOU'VE DONE,
HE COULD AT LEAST GIVE YOU
A PAT ON THE BACK.
- ( laughs )
HE ISN'T REALLY INTERESTED
IN HOW THE SAUSAGE GETS MADE.
THE OLD MAN WON'T SHOW THE
SLIGHTEST HINT OF SATISFACTION
UNTIL THIS SYSTEM
TURNS A PROFIT.
- SUPPLEMENTARY NAVIGATION
SATELLITES.
A PRIVATE ENTERPRISE
ALLOWED TO OVERSEE
GLOBAL DISTRIBUTION
UNDER THE ULTIMATE PRETEXT--
HELPING AMERICA.
CURRENTLY, G.P.S. UTILIZES
24 SATELLITES IN 6 ORBITS.
BUT WE CAN SUPPLEMENT THAT
FIVE TIMES OVER.
IT'LL GIVE US FULL CONTROL
OVER THE WORLD'S
DISTRIBUTION NETWORKS.
PLUS TRANSMISSIONS
AND COMMUNICATIONS!
- THAT KIND OF FLATTERY
MEANS NOTHING TO ME, MINAMI.
- FLATTERY WITHDRAWN.
- IGNITION SEQUENCE START.
SIX, FIVE,
FOUR, THREE...
- ALL ENGINES RUNNING.
- ...TWO, ONE.
- LIFT OFF.
- ( rap song playing )
- WAS IT A SUCCESS
OR A BUST?
- SHUT UP, MILDO!
- ANOTHER SUCCESSFUL LIFT-OFF.
- Schokolade:
WOW, WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT?
IT WAS TOTALLY WORTH
FOLLOWING DOCTOR MIAMI
ALL THE WAY OUT TO THE BOONIES,
SO WE COULD SEE THIS.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, BOONIES?
THAT'S INSENSITIVE
TOWARD THE NATIVES.
YOU DUMB-ASS BIMBO.
- ( cell phone ringing )
- COME ON,
WHO THE HELL'S CALLING NOW?
YEAH?
- ( laughs )
OH, CHIEF BLACK,
IT'S BEEN TOO LONG.
CAN I HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING?
- AGENT SCARECROW,
YOU'RE IN THE SOLOMONS,
RIGHT?
I DON'T GIVE A CRAP IF YOU WANT
TO HANG AROUND KOKO AND AMADA.
BUT I WARN YOU,
OPERATION UNDERSHAFT IS
STILL IN FULL EFFECT.
TRY NOT TO GET IN OUR WAY.
- WHAT?  SORRY, BOOKIE!
CAN'T HEAR A FRIGGIN' WORD
YOU'RE SAYIN'!
- HMM, STUPID PUNK.
HOW MANY ROCKETS
HAVE YOU MANAGED TO LAUNCH,
LITTLE LADY?
- LADIES AND GENTS,
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE LAUNCH
OF OUR 126th
AND FINAL ROCKET!
- ( all cheering )
- Man: WAS THAT IMPRESSIVE OR
WHAT?
- YOU COULD FEEL THE HEAT
FROM HERE.
- AMAZING, ISN'T IT, JONAH?
( laughs )
- Jonah ( thinking ):
AMIDST ALL THE EXCITEMENT...
THEY NEVER ONCE LOOKED UP
AT THE ROCKET.
WHAT COULD KOKO AND DR. MIAMI
HAVE BEEN DISCUSSING?
MAYBE IT WAS JUST
THE OMINOUS ROAR OF THE LAUNCH,
BUT THE TWO OF THEM LOOKED
ABSOLUTELY TERRIFYING TO ME.
- Miami: WHERE ARE YOU FOLKS
HEADED AFTER THIS?
- GOT A LITTLE TIME OFF,
THEN IT'S BACK TO BUSINESS.
BUT WE'RE NOT HEADING ANYWHERE
RIGHT THIS SECOND.
- IN THAT CASE, LET'S ALL
GO AND GRAB A FEW DRINKS.
HOW 'BOUT IT?
- HMM, WHY NOT?
WE CAN SLIP AWAY
LONG ENOUGH FOR THAT.
- All: YES!  YEAH!
- Koko: NO ONE BETTER
SNEAK JONAH ANY BOOZE!
- HELLO, JONAH.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO LEAVE MY SIDE, DON'T YOU?
- KOKO.
- PROMISE ME NO MATTER
HOW MUCH THE WORLD CHANGES,
YOU'LL ALWAYS STAY BY MY SIDE.
- Black: YOU'VE GOT ONE SHOT
TO INFILTRATE THEM.
AGENT RENATO,
OPERATION UNDERSHAFT IS A GO.
- Lehm: RENATO SOCCHI, GUESS
WE'RE GONNA BE WORKING TOGETHER.
I HEAR YOU WERE A LIEUTENANT
IN BERSAGLIERI INTELLIGENCE.
SO I EXPECT A LOT FROM YOU.
THERE'S A TOTAL
OF SIX BODYGUARDS
ON KOKO HEKMATYAR'S
PROTECTION DUTY.
THAT'S INCLUDING YOU, SO YOU'LL
HAVE TO CARRY YOUR WEIGHT.
- Koko: YOUR PREDECESSOR
RETIRED TO HEAVEN.
DON'T TRY TO FILL HIS SHOES,
BE EVEN BETTER THAN HE WAS.
YOU'RE EVEN MORE HANDSOME
THAN YOUR PHOTO.
I KNOW WHAT I'LL CALL YOU.
WELCOME ABOARD, R.
- I SWEAR I'LL DO MY BEST
TO KEEP YOU SAFE, LITTLE LADY.
( thinking )
I HAD RUN
A PRETTY THOROUGH BACKGROUND
CHECK ON HER.
BUT EVER SINCE THAT FIRST DAY
ON THE JOB,
WELL, MY IMAGE
OF KOKO HEKMATYAR CHANGED.
SHE BECAME THE LITTLE LADY
SHE IS NOW,
WITH THAT PERPETUAL SMILE
PLASTERED ON HER FACE.
IN OTHER WORDS, I'VE NEVER
SEEN THE REAL KOKO HEKMATYAR.
I SEE YOU STILL
HAVE A HEALTHY APPETITE.
GET ENOUGH TO EAT?
- WHAT ARE YOU, MY WIFE?
I'M HUNGRY
FROM ALL THAT WALKING.
SAVE YOUR WORRIES
FOR YOUR DRINKING.
DON'T GET SO TIPSY YOU
FORGET WHAT WAS SO URGENT
FOR YOU TO CALL ME HERE.
- IT SEEMS SOMEONE
AT THE COMPANY
WAS BACKING THOSE THREE
ASSASSINS I TOLD YOU ABOUT
THE OTHER DAY.
OR AS THE LITTLE LADY PUT IT,
"WHOEVER IT IS
THAT'S WATCHING US
ARE THE SAME PEOPLE
WHO HIRED THOSE GOONS."
- HA! SOUNDS LIKE SHE'S POINTING
THE FINGER SQUARE AT US.
THIS COULD GROW
AND BECOME A TUMOR.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
NOT FOR YOU AS MY AGENT,
AND NOT FOR ME
SINCE THIS WHOLE MISSION
WOULD COME TO A SCREECHING HALT
IF SHE EVER BEGAN TO DOUBT YOU.
KOKO'S TERMINATION
HAS NEVER BEEN A PART
OF OPERATION UNDERSHAFT.
IN FACT, WE NEED HER ALIVE.
IT WOULDN'T MAKE A LICK OF SENSE
FOR ME TO SEND ASSASSINS.
- WHICH IS WHY I DIDN'T THINK
YOU WERE BEHIND THIS, SAW.
HOWEVER...
- AN INSIDER?
- PROBABLY.
WE CAN'T AFFORD MORE
SUSPICIOUS INCIDENTS LIKE THIS.
I'LL BE FORCED
INTO EXPOSING MYSELF.
THE LITTLE LADY
WOULDN'T HESITATE
TO KILL ME IF SHE LEARNED
I WAS A TRAITOR.
AT MOST, SHE'D GIVE ME
FIVE SECONDS TO EXPLAIN,
IF I WAS LUCKY.
- UNDERSTOOD.
RELAX.
I'LL GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
- THANK YOU. MAYBE I CAN
FINALLY START TO BREATHE AGAIN.
- BEFORE I FORGET, SINCE WE SO
RARELY GET TO HAVE THESE CHATS,
I'VE GOT A QUESTION OF MY OWN.
AFTER SPENDING TWO YEARS
UNDERCOVER WITH HER,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF THE TARGET,
OUR SWEET LITTLE ARMS DEALER,
MISS HEKMATYAR?
- TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST, SAW,
I HAVE NO FUCKING CLUE.
THE WOMAN
DOES NOT REVEAL A THING.
SHE'S ABLE TO SHROUD HERSELF
AND ALL OF HER TRUE THOUGHTS
IN SOME KIND
OF IMPENETRABLE MIST.
IT REMINDS ME
OF WHEN I WAS IN BOSNIA,
GATHERING INTEL
ON ALL THOSE WARLORD SCUMBAGS.
SOME WERE SMART,
SOME WERE CHARISMATIC.
BUT INSIDE, THEIR HEARTS
WERE ALL PITCH BLACK.
SHE'S DIFFERENT, THOUGH.
REGARDLESS OF WHETHER
THE SITUATION IS BLACK OR WHITE,
SHE CONTINUES ON THE GRAY PATH.
SHE'S A MONSTER,
JUST SLITHERING ALONG
THAT FINE LINE
BETWEEN GOOD AND EVIL
AS SHE CONDUCTS HER BUSINESS.
AT THE SAME TIME,
SHE'S GOTTA BE
THE MOST BEAUTIFUL CRIMINAL
I'VE EVER SEEN.
REMEMBER THAT RUN-IN WE HAD
WITH THE BALKAN DRAGONS
IN THE REPUBLIC OF T?
AT ONE POINT,
THE LITTLE LADY COMPARED BALDRA
TO A MONSTER
OF OUR OWN CREATION.
TO WHICH, ONE OF THE DOCTORS
WE WERE ESCORTING REPLIED,
"MAYBE YOU'RE A DRAGON TOO."
- ( Black laughs )
- THE LITTLE LADY TRIED TO KEEP
HER COOL AND LAUGH IT OFF,
BUT HER ACTIONS
RIGHT AFTER THAT SEEMED A BIT,
I DON'T KNOW, OFF-BALANCE.
I SUSPECT SHE'S AWARE
THAT SHE'S BECOMING A MONSTER
AND SHE'S AFRAID
THAT ANY DAY NOW,
HER SUBORDINATES WILL SEE HER
FOR WHAT SHE IS AND ABANDON HER.
- HOW REFRESHINGLY HUMAN OF HER.
SO THERE'S THAT.
STILL, I'D RATHER
NOT SEE HER
TURN INTO AN UNCONTROLLABLE
BEAST, ALL THINGS CONSIDERED.
BUT WHAT CONCERNS ME THE MOST
IS HER INVOLVEMENT
WITH THAT KOOKY JAPANESE
SCIENTIST, MINAMI AMADA.
WHAT COULD THEY BE SCHEMING?
I'D SURE LIKE TO KNOW.
IF THEY CONTINUE TOGETHER,
THEY'LL BOTH BECOME MONSTERS
AT THE SAME TIME.
I FEEL IT IN MY GUT.
CAN'T REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
WE GOT TO DRINK THE NIGHT AWAY.
- OR, IN YOUR CASE,
EAT THE NIGHT AWAY, RIGHT?
- Both:
WELL, GUESS IT'S BACK TO WORK.
- R.
- HUH?
I WANT TO KNOW EXACTLY HOW MANY
ROCKETS SHE'S LAUNCHED SO FAR.
SEE YA.
( laughs )
- ( laughing ) YOU'RE ONE
CHEERFUL SON OF A BITCH.
- WHAT'S UP, JONAH?
YOU BORED?
- NO.
THE OCEAN'S PRETTY.
- SEA.
THE AEGEAN SEA.
- MMM.
- THE C.I.A. HAS FOUR DISTINCT
TYPES OF POSITION
THAT OVERSEE THEIR SPIES.
FIRST ARE THE SUPERVISORS
IN CHARGE OF GATHERING INTEL.
THOSE GUYS ARE CALLED
COLLECTION MANAGEMENT OFFICERS.
THEN THERE'S THE ONES
WHO ASSIST OPERATIVES.
THOSE ARE
STAFF OPERATIONS OFFICERS.
THE PEOPLE WHO DIRECTLY MANAGE
OPERATIONS ARE CASE OFFICERS.
AND THE ONES
WHO OVERSEE MILITARY-STYLE OPS
ARE KNOWN AS PARAMILITARY
OPERATIONS OFFICERS.
- WHY ARE YOU TELLIN' ME THIS?
DOES IT HAVE TO DO WITH
SCARECROW WORKING
FOR THE C.I.A.?
- SURE DOES. SEE, THAT
NUISANCE IS A CASE OFFICER.
HE'S IN THE FIELD,
SUPERVISING MISSIONS.
I KNOW IT'S CONFUSING,
BUT YOU GOTTA LEARN THIS STUFF.
NORMAL KIDS YOUR AGE
GET TO WORRY ABOUT
MUCH MORE TRIVIAL THINGS,
BUT YOU'RE WITH US NOW, JONAH.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
I'M GIVING YOU A CRASH COURSE
ON THE C.I.A.
BECAUSE YOU NEED TO KNOW
WHAT WE'RE UP AGAINST.
THE FIRST TWO TYPES
ARE HOLED UP
AT THEIR HEADQUARTERS
IN LANGLEY,
SO WE RARELY CROSS
PATHS WITH THEM.
BUT THE KIND THAT MAKE ME
WANNA TURN AND RUN
WHEN I ENCOUNTER THEM
IN THE FIELD IS THE P.O.O.--
THE PARAMILITARY.
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO CARRY OUT
THE AGENCY'S COMBAT OPERATIONS.
NOT SURPRISINGLY,
MOST OF 'EM WERE RECRUITED
FROM SPECIAL FORCES.
THEY REQUISITION WEAPONS,
CONDUCT RAIDS
AND SPRING AMBUSHES.
THEY'RE EXPERTS IN EXPLOSIVES,
ABDUCTION, IMPRISONMENT,
TORTURE, AND SO ON.
YOU GET THE PICTURE?
THAT'S WHY WE TEND TO CLASH
WITH THEM MORE THAN I'D LIKE.
BUT WE'RE AS MUCH A THORN IN
THEIR SIDE AS THEY ARE IN OURS.
OF COURSE, THE REASON
I'M TELLING YOU ALL THIS NOW
IS THAT LAST BUNCH OF HIT MEN--
TOTAL FREAKS.
I KNOW YOU DIDN'T SEE THEM.
BUT IT'S HIGHLY LIKELY THEY
WERE SENT TO KILL ME BY A P.O.O.
- WAS IT SOMEONE YOU KNOW?
- CAN'T SAY FOR SURE.
THERE'S PLENTY OF PEOPLE
WHO WANT ME DEAD.
BUT THERE IS ONE WHO HATES ME
MORE THAN THE REST.
DAMN IT, HEX.
WHY CAN'T THEY JUST FIND YOU
DEAD IN A DITCH SOMEWHERE?
- WAIT OUT HERE FOR ME, FELLAS.
I WON'T BE LONG.
- THE FUCK, HEX?
- HEY THERE.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE, HASN'T IT,
SPIN?
YOU'RE RAKING IT IN.
- WHAT ON EARTH ARE
YOU DOING HERE?
EVER HEAR
OF MAKING AN APPOINTMENT?
IT'S OKAY, GUYS.
FALL BACK.
- SIR? BUT SHE COULD--
- I TELL YOU TO LEAVE,
YOU LEAVE!
YOU GOT A DEATH WISH?
- HEX?
WHAT, LIKE A HEXAGON?
- NAH, IT'S GERMAN.
SHORT FOR, LIKE, WITCH.
- CATCH ME UP.
LAST I HEARD,
YOU WERE STILL IN AFGHANISTAN.
- I AM. BUT IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THE AFGHANISTAN JOB
BROUGHT ME HERE TO BUDAPEST.
AND SINCE WE GO WAY BACK,
I HOPED YOU'D BE ABLE
TO FILL ME IN ON SOMETHING.
- COME ON!
YOU KNOW I CAN'T TELL YOU SQUAT.
I'VE GOT UNOFFICIAL COVER HERE.
AN EXEC
IN THE TRADING INDUSTRY,
WHICH MEANS
NO DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY.
SO PLEASE, GET LOST.
- GOODNESS.
YOU'RE KICKING ME OUT BEFORE YOU
EVEN HEAR WHAT I HAVE TO SAY.
THEY'VE GOT ME ASSIGNED ME
TO YOUR JOB TOO,
SO WHY NOT LOOSEN UP AND SLIP ME
A COUPLE OF DETAILS?
- HEX, DON'T.
- TELL ME,
WHY ARE YOU FELLAS
ALWAYS SO HARD ON ME?
I'M JUST LIKE YOU,
TRYING TO SERVE MY COUNTRY.
- YOU REALLY WANNA KNOW?
IT'S 'CAUSE
YOU TAKE EVERYTHING TOO FAR.
EVERYONE'S SCARED OF YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE A
TICKING TIME BOMB.
YOU'RE THE GESTAPO
MEETS THE CHEKA IN HIGH HEELS.
THAT CUTTHROAT SQUAD
YOU RUN'S ILLEGALLY KILLED
COUNTLESS
TERROR SUSPECTS--
- TELL ME
ABOUT OPERATION UNDERSHAFT.
- UNDERSHAFT IS THE NAME
OF A BRILLIANT,
BUT UNSCRUPULOUS ARMS DEALER
IN A GEORGE BERNARD SHAW PLAY.
- I KNOW THAT.
NOW WHAT'S THE NAME OF
OUR TARGET ARMS DEALER?
- ( groans )
YEAH.
(laughs)
OPERATION UNDERSHAFT
IS THE COMPANY'S PLOT
TO TURN KOKO HEKMATYAR
INTO OUR ARMS-DEALING PUPPET.
H.C.L.I. HAS BECOME
A GIANT IN OVERSEAS
TRANSPORTATION AND LOGISTICS.
SO THE OBJECTIVE IS TO PIGGYBACK
OFF THEIR INTEL NETWORK
AND AUGMENT THE MILITARY'S
OWN COMM SYSTEMS.
WE LATCHED ONTO KOKO
'CAUSE SHE'S THE YOUNGEST
IN THAT FAMILY.
THAT WAS THE BRAINCHILD
OF THE MAN IN CHARGE OF THIS,
BOOK MAN.
- ( laughs )
SO SHE WAS THE TARGET ALL ALONG?
KOKO HEKMATYAR?
( laughs ) THAT SLY OLD BASTARD
KNEW KOKO AND I
HAD A COMPLICATED PAST,
SO HE USED ME
AS HIS NAIVE ERRAND
GIRL TO BLINDLY LAY
THE GROUNDWORK
FOR HIS OPERATION.
( laughs ) DAMN IT, IT'S NOT
FUNNY.
SOME TRAGIC SHIT WENT DOWN
BETWEEN US BACK IN THE DAY.
SO I TOOK IT UPON MYSELF
TO SEND SOME HIT MEN AS A GIFT.
IT WAS JUST A FRIENDLY WARM-UP.
BUT IT SEEMS
I'VE STIRRED THE POT
JUST AS PEOPLE WERE GETTING
ANTSY ABOUT UNDERSHAFT.
GOOD THING YOU WERE
KIND ENOUGH TO CONFIRM
WHO'S STANDING IN MY WAY.
AND NOW, MY DEAREST KOKO,
I'LL KILL YOU.
- YOU'RE REALLY GOIN'
AGAINST BOOK MAN?
GET YOUR ASS OFF!
COME ON, HEX.
I'M BEGGIN' YOU, PLEASE.
- WHICH IS IT?
WANT ME TO GET OFF
OR YOU WANT ME TO LEAVE?
- ( groans )
- ( laughs ) GUESS THAT
ANSWERS MY QUESTION.
( laughs )
PEOPLE ARE DESTINED TO DIE,
AND YET,
THEY REFUSE TO FIGHT.
WHY EVEN BOTHER BEING BORN?
- I HAD A QUIET AFTERNOON ALONE.
DIDN'T SEE ANYONE OR ANYTHING.
- GOOD BOY. 'CAUSE IF I FIND
OUT YOU'VE TATTLED ON ME, SPIN,
I'LL KILL YOU TOO.
HOW'S #24 TODAY?
- Man: THE DETAINEE?
HE WON'T TALK, MA'AM.
WHAT DO YOU WANT US TO DO?
- ( panting )
- ALL YOU GOTTA DO
IS TELL US YOUR FRIENDS' NAMES.
- (groans) GO TO HELL,
YOU FUCKING WITCH!
- ( gun fires )
- JUST PUTTING A BULLET
IN KOKO WON'T BE ANY FUN.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT IN THIS WORLD
WOULD HURT HER MOST
AND THEN DESTROY IT.
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪