- MINAMI,
YOU'RE MY ONE TRUE FRIEND
AND THE ONLY PERSON I TRUST.
ISN'T THAT NICE TO HEAR?
- WHAT?
WHY ARE YOU SAYING THIS NOW?
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN BESTIES.
WE CATCH BUTTERFLIES.
IN FACT, I BET I'M
YOUR ONLY FRIEND.
HECK, I WAS IN THE SAME
BOAT BEFORE WE MET.
BUT REGARDLESS OF THE REASON,
YES, THAT IS NICE TO HEAR, KOKO.
OH!  A NEW SPECIES
I'VE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
- LET'S NOT BE SUICIDAL.
- I WISH I COULD FLY.
THEN I COULD HAVE A COMPLETE
COLLECTION OF EVERY SPECIES.
- I THINK IT'S A GOOD THING
THAT HUMANS CAN'T FLY.
NOW STEP BACK.
- BUMMER.
I'M PRETTY SURE THAT WAS
AN UNCLASSIFIED SPECIMEN.
KOKO, WOULD YOU SAY THE TWO
OF US ARE GENIUSES?
- YOU DEFINITELY ARE, MINAMI,
BUT I WOULDN'T CALL MYSELF
A GENIUS AT ANYTHING.
- EXCEPT ARMS DEALING.
OH, DON'T POUT, KOKO.
YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT OR DO YOU
REALLY THINK GREEDY POLITICIANS
AND MILITIAS BUY FROM YOU JUST
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE DAUGHTER
OF SOME NOTORIOUS
SHIPPING MAGNATE?
OR YOU'RE YOUNG AND CAN PLAY
THE SWEET AND INNOCENT ROUTINE?
NO, IT'S BECAUSE YOU EXCEL
AT EARNING PEOPLE'S TRUST.
BETWEEN MY BRAINS
AND YOUR BUSINESS ACUMEN,
I'M POSITIVE WE'LL MAKE
YOUR DREAM A REALITY.
- YEAH, KEEP IT DOWN,
WOULD YOU?
WE'RE THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE ALIVE
WHO KNOW ABOUT THIS PLAN
AND I'D LIKE
TO KEEP IT THAT WAY.
THAT MEANS WE CAN ONLY
CONFIDE IN THE DEAD.
CAN YOU SEE IT?  THE WORLD WE'VE
DREAMED FINALLY BECOMING REAL?
- YES, I SEE IT!
I WANT TO LIVE IN THE NEW
WORLD YOU CREATE, KOKO.
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO.
- YOU AND I ARE BUILDING
THIS WORLD TOGETHER.
- YOU KNOW I'M GONNA HOLD YOU
TO THAT, RIGHT?
I HATE WHEN PEOPLE GET BORED
HALFWAY THROUGH AND QUIT.
- I WANT YOU THINKING ABOUT
THE PLAN AT ALL TIMES NOW,
EVEN IN YOUR SLEEP.
YOUR FIRST TASK IS GETTING ME AN
ITEMIZED LIST OF START-UP COSTS.
I'LL COVER THEM IN FULL.
- OKAY.
DIDN'T CATCH A SINGLE ONE.
HMM, LET'S HEAD BACK.
OH, ALSO...
I HATE WHEN PEOPLE GET PUSHY.
- WHAT?!
- YEAH, PUSH ME TOO HARD AND
I MIGHT QUIT HALFWAY THROUGH.
- NOW YOU'RE JUST
BEING DIFFICULT.
- ( laughing )
- ( theme music playing )
- LET'S HEAR IT FOR
THE SUCCESSFUL COMPLETION
OF MÄRCHEN'S LATEST FACTORY.
- YEAH!
- ( cheering )
THIS FACILITY WOULD HAVE
NEVER BEEN POSSIBLE
WITHOUT THE GENEROUS FUNDING
OF ME, KOKO HEKMATYAR,
OR THE TECHNICAL EXPERTISE
OF OUR HEAD OF TOY AND ROBOT
RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT,
MY BEST FRIEND, MINAMI.
- IT ALSO HAS A HOT SPRING.
- WHAT?
YOU CHANGED THE BLUEPRINTS
WITHOUT TELLING ME AGAIN?
- I CAN'T BE EXPECTED TO COME UP
WITH GREAT IDEAS
IF I DON'T HAVE
A GOOD SOAK FIRST.
- MINAMI!
- ( all laughing )
- OOH!  OOH!
THIS IS SHAPING UP
TO BE A STICKY SITUATION.
- Scarecrow: YES, SCHOKOLADE?
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT AM I DOING IN ENGLAND?
YOU DO REALIZE I HAVE OTHER
CASES TO WORK, DON'T YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU, DENSE?
I CAN'T TAIL PROFESSOR
AMADA ALL YEAR.
JUST CUT TO THE CHASE.
WHAT?  HEKMATYAR SHOWED UP
FOR THE OPENING
OF AMADA'S
NEW MÄRCHEN FACILITY?!
- YEAH.  SHE AND HER WHOLE UNIT
OF BAD-ASSES ARE HERE.
LIKE THEY'RE THROWING A PARTY.
RECORD THEM?
I CAN'T GET THAT CLOSE NOW.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
THIS WAS GOING DOWN.
PLANTING BUGS TAKES TIME.
- FOR CHRIST SAKES,
JUST GIVE THAT JONAH KID
SOME CANDY OR SOMETHING
PLANT A BUG ON HIM.
- YOU'RE BANANAS.
- FRIGGIN' KOKO.
WHAT THE HELL DOES SHE EVEN NEED
WITH A TOY FACTORY IN AFRICA?
IF IT EVEN IS A TOY FACTORY.
DUH!
OKAY, HERE'S A PLAN.
WALK UP AND ASK, "HEY, GUYS.
WHAT YOU MAKING IN HERE?"
THEY SEEM TO LIKE YOU,
SO I DOUBT YOU'LL GET SHOT.
- YEAH, NO.
YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
- FUCK ME.  I'M SURE NOW
I'M GONNA GET A CALL
FROM THAT FAT-ASS MR. BOOKMAN
ABOUT ALL THIS.
- Black: KOKO WAS AT THE OPENING
OF THE NEW MÄRCHEN FACTORY?
ODD.  OUR INTEL SAID SHE'D BE
IN FRANCE.
THE LITTLE LADY SURE LIKES
KEEPING ME ON MY TOES.
SHOULD HAVE EXPECTED THIS
KIND OF THING.
HELLO, SCARECROW.
YOU'RE ON THAT SIDE
OF THE WORLD.
MIND TELLING ME WHAT'S UP
IN SOUTH AFRICA?
- SORRY, CHIEF BLACK.
LAST TIME I CHECKED,
I DON'T WORK FOR YOU.
- JUST ANSWER THE QUESTION.
- I DON'T KNOW, ALL RIGHT?
NORMALLY, THERE'S A HANDFUL
OF PMC THUGS GUARDING THE PLACE.
WEIRD FOR A TOY FACTORY,
I GUESS, BUT NOT THAT WEIRD.
NOW I'M HEARING HEKMATYAR
AND HER SQUAD ARE THERE,
BUT ONLY PROFESSOR AMADA
GOES IN OR OUT.
SINCE I'M A NICE GUY,
I'LL KEEP INVESTIGATING
AND FILL YOU IN
IF I GET A BREAK.
- SO COOL.  IT'S LIKE
DR. MIAMI'S PRIVATE CASTLE.
- GOOD.  THANK YOU.
I LOOK FORWARD TO HEARING BACK.
- ( beeps )
- Jonah: YOU SURVIVED, HUH?
- SURE DID.
- YOU WERE WITH US
FOR THE ROCKET LAUNCH, TOO.
DOES THAT MEAN YOU'VE STARTED
WORKING FOR DR. MIAMI?
- YEAH, THAT'S ABOUT THE SIZE
OF IT.
- Mao: A TOY FACTORY, HUH?
- I DON'T THINK I'LL EVER FIGURE
OUT HOW THE LADY'S MIND WORKS.
- HANG ON.
WHERE'S MINAMI AND JONAH?
- DOCTOR, YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- OF COURSE, DON'T SWEAT IT.
JONAH WOULD BE BORED STIFF
JUST HANGING AROUND
THE FACTORY ALL DAY.
- Jonah: ISN'T THE WEATHER
A LITTLE COLD FOR BUTTERFLIES?
- KOKO'S RIGHT.
HE'S NOT MUCH OF A TALKER,
BUT AT LEAST HE CAME WITH.
THAT'S GOOD.
TACITURN KAREN
AND DEAD-SERIOUS JONAH,
WHAT WERE YOU TWO DISCUSSING
EARLIER?
- WE DISCUSSED OUR PAST.
- I SHOT KAREN MULTIPLE TIMES.
- ( laughs )
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, JONAH.
THE PAST IS THE PAST.
BESIDES, KAREN'S A TOUGH COOKIE.
YOU'RE RIGHT, JONAH.
I DON'T SEE A SINGLE BUG.
NO BIGGIE.  THE IMPORTANT THING
IS WE ALL GOT OUT FOR A WALK.
- Jonah: DR. MIAMI,
MAY I ASK A QUESTION?
- WELL, OF COURSE.
I LOVE A GOOD QUESTION.
I'LL ANSWER ANYTHING,
WITH ONE MINOR EXCEPTION.
- WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU
AND KOKO UP TO HERE?
- SORRY, JONAH,
THAT WOULD BE THE EXCEPTION.
KEEPING OUR PLAN A SECRET
IS THE BIGGEST PROMISE
I'VE EVER MADE TO KOKO.
- OH, IT'S COOL.
- JONAH, PLEASE COME PLAY AGAIN
SOMETIME SOON.
- WOW, SUCH A CUTIE.
I WANT A JONAH.
- HELL NO.
- HEY, DON'T GET MAD.
I THINK IT'D BE GOOD FOR JONAH
TO STAY WITH ME FOR A WHILE.
- AND WHY IS THAT?
- I'M WORRIED THAT CUTENESS IS
GONNA EAT YOUR HARD EXTERIOR
AND TURN YOU INTO A BIG SOFTY.
DON'T GIVE ME THAT LOOK.
- I'M SORRY.
YOU THREW ME FOR A SECOND.
MOSTLY I WAS SURPRISED
YOU'D EVEN ALLOW YOURSELF
TO ENTERTAIN SUCH WARM,
FUZZY THOUGHTS.
SOMEONE SO GOOD
AT BEING DISCONNECTED,
NOTICING PEOPLE'S SOFT SPOTS.
IT'S A NICE CHANGE.
IT TELLS ME YOU'RE TAKING
THE PLAN SERIOUSLY
AS IT BECOMES MORE REAL.
SO ALONG WITH THAT,
YOU'RE LOOKING AT HOW OUR
ACTIONS AFFECT OTHERS.
YOU'RE SCARED,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING TO FEAR.
WE HAVE ONLY ONE MORE STEP
BEFORE OUR PLAN'S COMPLETE.
WE NEED THE PART
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE.
THE WHEELS ARE IN MOTION
AND THEY CANNOT BE STOPPED.
GRANTED, THERE'S A CHANCE THOSE
WITH THE KEENEST OF INTUITION
MIGHT FIGURE OUT
WHAT WE'RE UP TO.
MANY WILL WANT WHAT WE'RE
MAKING FOR THEMSELVES,
AND MANY WILL WANT
IT DESTROYED,
BUT AS LONG AS
WE KEEP THEM GUESSING,
WE CAN PLAY THOSE SIDES
AGAINST EACH OTHER.
THAT'S WHY NO ONE IS GOING TO
MAKE A MOVE AGAINST US.
- ( laughs )
I HOPE NOT.
THIS HAD BETTER WORK.
- I'M 100% SURE IT WILL,
PROFESSOR AMADA.
LOOK AT THE TIME.  GOTTA GO.
- NO SLACKING
ON THE JOB, MINAMI.
- AW, NO FAIR.
THEY LOOK SO SOFT.
- SHE'S SURE SETTLED INTO
THE ROLE OF "EVIL ARMS DEALER."
- SORRY, DOCTOR, BUT CUDDLING'S
NOT IN MY JOB DESCRIPTION.
- HEY, YOU NEVER KNOW.
OH, RIGHT.
KOKO, CAN WE FINALLY
GIVE A NAME
TO THIS BIG SECRET
PROJECT OF OURS?
I'M TIRED
OF CALLING IT "THE PLAN."
- IT'S JORMUNGAND.
THE PLAN IS JORMUNGAND.
- JORMUNGAND, THE WORLD SERPENT.
SNARKY.  I LIKE IT.
( laughs )
- DR. AMADA, SOMETHING AMUSING
YOU'D CARE TO SHARE WITH US?
- SORRY, MR. CURRY,
JUST AN OLD INSIDE JOKE.
IT'S NOT REALLY
APPROPRIATE TO SHARE.
ANYWAY, I APPRECIATE YOU
ROLLING OUT THE RED CARPET
AND TREATING ME TO THIS
DELICIOUS FEAST,
BUT I DON'T THINK I CAN GIVE
YOU MUCH HELP IN RETURN.
IT WON'T GO WELL FOR YOU IF YOU
ASK ME TO MAKE YOU A WEAPON.
THANKFULLY, I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
STUPID ENOUGH TO DO SO.
- I APPRECIATE THAT.
- ALL MR. CURRY WANTS TO KNOW
IS WHAT YOU
AND YOUR FRIEND KOKO
ARE DOING,
YOU KNOW, WITH THAT NEW MÄRCHEN
FACILITY YOU OPENED.
- KOKO?  YOU'RE FRIENDS
WITH HER.  ASK HER YOURSELVES.
- MILDO, SHUT YOUR GOB,
WILL YOU?
FORGIVE ME, DOCTOR, THAT'S NOT
WHY WE ASKED YOU HERE.
GRANTED, I'D BE LYING
IF I SAID I WASN'T CURIOUS,
BUT I KNOW YOU'RE MUCH
TOO SMART TO EVER TELL ME.
THEN WHAT THE BLOODY HELL ARE WE
DOING IN SOUTH AFRICA, HUH??
- OOH, SHE HAS ZERO FILTER.
I LIKE HER.
- THERE IS ONE THING, THOUGH.
I'M CURIOUS ABOUT THE MARKET'S
ABILITY TO STILL SUPPORT
MID-SIZED DEALERS LIKE MYSELF.
- THOSE WITH THE KEENEST
OF INTUITION MIGHT FIGURE OUT.
- WHAT?  MR. CURRY,
IS THE COMPANY GOING UNDER?
AM I LOSING MY JOB?
- I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I KNOW
ABOUT CURRY'S AIR TRANSPORT.
- AS A YOUNG MAN, MR. CURRY,
YOU WERE AN ACE PILOT
IN THE ROYAL AIR FORCE.
WHEN YOU RETIRED,
YOU BOUGHT AN OLD FREIGHTER
AND STARTED A LESS THAN
LEGITIMATE CARGO COMPANY.
SOON OTHER OFFICERS LENT YOU
THEIR PLANES AND RUNWAYS,
KNOWING FULL WELL WHAT BUSINESS
YOU WERE IN.
- DOCTOR, YOU FLATTER ME.
THOUGH YOU MAKE WHAT
WE DO SOUND SO BAD.
YOU'VE DONE YOUR RESEARCH.
- NOT REALLY.
THAT'S JUST WHAT KOKO TOLD ME.
I TAKE IT FROM YOUR FIRST
QUESTION YOU'RE STRUGGLING.
AIR FUEL COSTS HAVE BEEN
ON THE RISE EVERY YEAR,
SO MUCH SO THAT YOU'RE NOW
SPENDING MORE SHIPPING WEAPONS
THAN YOU CAN MAKE SELLING THEM.
AND WITH THE DEMAND FOR COLD
WAR-ERA WEAPONS DRYING UP,
AUTHORITIES ARE TURNING
ON YOUR RIVAL DEALERS,
AS THEIR SERVICES
ARE NO LONGER NEEDED.
THERE'S BEEN A SHIFT
IN WHO PROFITS FROM WAR.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
- MR. CURRY,
I WON'T LET THEM GET TO YOU.
- MILDO!
- I DON'T KNOW.
THIS YEAR COULD GET
PRETTY ROUGH FOR HIM.
- LISTEN, DOC, KEEP TALKING
LIKE THAT AND YOU'LL GET
YOUR SKULL BASHED IN.
- MILDO!
- NO, NO GUNS, KAREN.
IN FACT, WHY DON'T YOU
HAND IT OVER TO MILDO?
- YES, DOCTOR.
- OI, I'VE HEARD OF YOU.
YOU LOST A DUEL TO VALMET.
- AND NOW YOU WANNA TRY ME?
- ( grunting )
- KOKO BELIEVES WAR FINALLY
BECAME PRIVATIZED THIS CENTURY
WHEN GOVERNMENTS REALIZED THE
TRUE COSTS NEEDED TO WAGE IT.
BUT IF WAR'S A BUSINESS,
IT'S SUBJECT TO MARKET FORCES.
- THE PROBLEM WITH ALL THAT IS
THAT THE MARKET IS DRYING UP.
LESS NAPALM IN THE JUNGLES,
LESS OIL IN THE DESERT,
FEWER BATTLEFIELDS REEKING
OF GUNPOWDER,
BUT WAR BREEDS AN ENDLESS CYCLE
OF POVERTY AND DEBT.
SOLDIERS TAKE TO THE FIELD
WITH QUESTION MARKS
HANGING ABOVE THEIR HEADS.
ALL THE WHILE WHAT OFFICIAL WAR
IS LEFT WILL BE FOUGHT
BY BUTTON PUSHERS
IN AIR-CONDITIONED OFFICES,
VIA DRONES HIGH IN THE SKY.
WAR'S NOTHING LIKE IT ONCE WAS.
- WELL, FOR BETTER OR WORSE,
THE WARS AND BATTLEFIELDS
YOU'VE SURVIVED AND PROFITED
FROM AREN'T COMING BACK.
CAN YOU AFFORD
TO BE LEFT BEHIND?
LET ME BE BLUNT,
PRESIDENT CURRY.
YOU SHOULD HAVE MADE THIS
DECISION ABOUT YOUR FUTURE
LONG BEFORE YOU WASTED MONEY
INVITING AN OUTSIDER
LIKE ME TO DINNER.
THE CLEAR CHOICE IS TO LEAVE
THE GUN TRADE TO KOKO.
- ( laughs )
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO RESPOND
TO THAT, DOCTOR.
I RECOGNIZE MY TIME'S PASSED,
BUT I CAN'T GIVE UP.
AT LEAST,
NOT RIGHT TO KOKO'S FACE.
SO WHAT KIND OF BUSINESS
DO YOU SUGGEST I GO INTO?
- YOU COULD START A RESTAURANT.
- I DO LIKE TO COOK, SIR.
- YOU REALLY LIKE THAT
KIND OF WORK, LOU?
- OF COURSE, SIR.
- ( groaning )
I GIVE UP.
YOU BEAT ME.
I WANNA HELP WITH YOUR NEW
RESTAURANT VENTURE, MR. CURRY.
- THAT'S NICE, MILDO.
SIT DOWN.
AND DO TRY TO BEHAVE YOURSELF.
- UGH, I ATE SO MUCH.
DRANK TOO.
KAREN, YOU ARE ONE
TOUGH COOKIE.
IS YOUR HAND OKAY?
- CONSIDERING HOW THICK
HER SKULL IS, I'M FINE.
- HIS WAY OF GIVING UP WAS
LETTING YOU TRASH MILDO.
ARMS DEALERS SURE ARE WEIRD.
I GUESS, WHEN YOU'VE MADE A
FORTUNE PROVIDING YOUR CUSTOMERS
WITH THE TOOLS TO KILL PEOPLE,
YOU START TO GO A LITTLE CUCKOO
IN THE COCONUT.
- Koko: JONAH, ISN'T THE VIEW
OUT HERE PRETTY AT NIGHT?
MAN, THE ONLY THING BETTER IS
FINALLY HAVING THIS CAR BACK.
UGO WAS SO EXCITED,
HE SQUEALED LIKE A GIRL.
TAKES YOU BACK, HUH?
REMINDS ME OF THE DAY
YOU AND I FIRST MET.
I EVEN TOOK YOU ON A DRIVE
IN THIS VERY CAR
JUST SO WE COULD BOND A LITTLE.
JONAH?
MORE THINGS CHANGE,
THE MORE THEY STAY THE SAME.
HELLO, JONAH.
JONAH.
- ( sighs )
KOKO, ALL THIS GRABBING MAKES IT
HARDER FOR ME TO PROTECT YOU.
- GOODY.  YOU'RE FINALLY GETTING
BACK TO YOUR SURLY OLD SELF.
- ALTHOUGH, I DO HAVE TO AGREE
WITH HIM ABOUT THE GRABBINESS.
- POOR VALMET.
GETTING A LITTLE JELLY THERE.
- MY DEAR KOKO.
ONCE AGAIN,
IT HAS BEEN FAR TOO LONG.
I EVEN THOUGHT ABOUT JOINING
YOUR FAMILY'S COMPANY
SO WE'D HAVE A CHANCE
TO SPEND MORE TIME TOGETHER.
- IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU,
TOO, MS. TOROHOVSKY.
- Black: HEKMATYAR AND
TOROHOVSKY ARE MEETING AGAIN?
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
BOTH LADIES ARE DOING WELL
FOR THEMSELVES
I'VE BEEN TOLD HEKMATYAR'S
WANTED A DEAL WITH HER
FOR A WHILE.
I HEAR SHE WANTS
THREE LAST-GEN UAVs
ALONG WITH THEIR SUPPORT STAFFS.
SHE'LL PROBABLY JUST LEASE
THEM TO SOMEONE IN AFRICA.
SEEMS EVEN GUERRILLA GROUPS
ARE USING 'EM THESE DAYS.
- ( vibrating )
- YEAH.
- Black: SCARECROW,
WHAT'S YOUR LOCATION?
- JUST ARRIVED IN SOUTH AFRICA.
- WHY ARE YOU THERE?
- I'M HERE FOR THE STUPID AMADA
THING WE TALKED ABOUT.
ROOTIN' AROUND HER FINANCES
TO SEE WHERE SHE'S GETTING MONEY
FOR THAT FANCY FACTORY.
- VERY WELL.  KEEP ON IT.
- "KEEP ON IT," HE SAYS.
HOW MANY TIMES I GOTTA REMIND
YOU YOU'RE NOT MY DAMN BOSS?
- OH, WAS THAT BOOK MAN?
- SHUT UP.
- HE'S REALLY STARTED PULLING
YOUR STRINGS, HASN'T HE?
- I SAID SHUT UP!
- ( laughing )
- Man: BOOK MAN, WE NEED YOU
IN THE CONFERENCE ROOM.
THE BROADCAST OF KASPER'S
SPEECH IS ABOUT TO START.
- RIGHT.  ON MY WAY.
HCLI SEEMS TO BE RUNNING
AT FULL STEAM THESE DAYS.
SURE HOPE THEY CAN HANDLE IT.
WOULDN'T WANT 'EM TO BLOW A HOLE
IN THE BOTTOM OF THEIR OWN SHIP.
I'M ALONG FOR THIS RIDE,
TOO, AFTER ALL.
- LOOK UP AT THE SKY
AND SAY, "PEACE."
- PEACE.
- WHOA.
- THIS IS THE STILL IMAGE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A DRONE PHOTO
WITH SUCH GREAT RESOLUTION
FROM THAT HIGH UP.
- Amalia: THE OPTICS ARE WHAT
MAKES THIS MODEL SO SPECIAL.
- OUR COMPANY'S ALSO CREATED
AN ULTRA-LIGHT, HIGH-FLYING UAV
WITH SOLAR PANELS
ON ITS WINGS.
IT CHARGES DURING THE DAY
AND RUNS OFF BATTERIES AT NIGHT,
MAKING IT POSSIBLE
TO CIRCLE A TARGET FOR DAYS.
IN FACT, WITH NEXT-GEN
BATTERIES,
IT'LL BE POSSIBLE FOR US
TO MAKE A UAV
THAT CAN STAY UP THERE
FOR YEARS.
- I AM SORRY TO INTERRUPT,
AMALIA.
THE BROADCAST
OF KASPER HEKMATYAR'S SPEECH
FROM THE PHILIPPINES
IS ABOUT TO BEGIN.
- I ALMOST FORGOT.  WILL YOU
RECORD IT FOR ME, PLEASE?
- OF COURSE, MA'AM.
- YOU SURE YOU CAN WAIT?
- I AM CURIOUS.
I HEAR YOUR BROTHER'S USING
THE WEAPONS EXPO AS A PLATFORM
FOR A BIG ANNOUNCEMENT.
SEEMS THERE'S SOMETHING
NEW IN THE WORKS.
I WONDER IF IT IS RELATED
TO THOSE SATELLITES
YOU'VE BEEN LAUNCHING.
PERHAPS SOMETHING
THAT'LL REVOLUTIONIZE
GLOBAL DISTRIBUTION,
CHANGE THE ARMS TRADE,
WHICH WOULD PROBABLY CHANGE
THE WAY WARS ARE FOUGHT.
PEOPLE MIGHT WONDER WHY THEY
NEED ARMS DEALERS LIKE US.
HOWEVER, SOMETHING TELLS ME
TALKING WITH YOU RIGHT NOW
WILL PROVE FAR MORE PROFITABLE
IN THE LONG RUN.
AT LEAST,
THAT'S THE FEELING I GET.
- ( chattering )
- GOOD AFTERNOON ASSEMBLED
OFFICERS, CONTRACTORS
AND DEFENSE EMPLOYEES.
MY NAME IS KASPER HEKMATYAR.
HEY, COME ON FOLKS, WAKE UP!
I'M WORRIED YOU'RE
GONNA PUT ME TO SLEEP.
I'M SURE MANY OF YOU HAVE
WORKED WITH ME BEFORE.
BECAUSE OF THAT, WHEN IT COMES
TO WEAPONS, I'M JUST A DEALER.
SO FOR THIS PROJECT,
CONSIDER ME A SPOKESMAN,
RATHER THAN AN ENGINEER.
IF YOU HAVE ANY TECHNICAL
QUESTIONS, PLEASE LOOK
AT THE BROCHURES PROVIDED
OR CALL OUR HOME OFFICE.
- KASPER HEKMATYAR IS ONE
APATHETIC SPOKESMAN.
I CAN SEE HOW
THEY'RE SIBLINGS.
- NOW LET'S GET TO THE REASON
YOU'RE HERE
THE HEKMATYAR GLOBAL GRID
IS A COMPREHENSIVE LOGISTICS
AND COMMAND TRANSMISSION
PACKAGE,
OUTSOURCED
TO THE PRIVATE SECTOR.
CUSTOMERS WILL BENEFIT
FROM HCLI'S INTEGRATED
WORLDWIDE FREIGHT NETWORK,
WHILE OUR SYSTEM
OF 126 SATELLITES PROVIDES THEM
WITH UNPRECEDENTED
REAL-TIME DATA.
SINCE THE TIME OF ROME,
THE ARMY HAS BEEN A DOG
HELD BACK BY THE CHAIN
OF LOGISTICS.
IT'S A CHAIN THAT LIMITS
MOVEMENT AND FREEDOM,
WHILE AT THE SAME TIME,
SERVING AS A LIFELINE.
SUPPLY DISTRIBUTION,
COMMUNICATION, MAINTENANCE,
BASE CONSTRUCTION, EVEN THE
MOST HIGHLY TRAINED SOLDIER
WILL BE CRIPPLED IF YOU STRIP
AWAY ONLY ONE OF THESE.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS ALL COSTS
A BOATLOAD OF MONEY.
SO HOW DO YOU KEEP SOLDIERS
ALIVE WITHOUT KILLING FINANCES?
STREAMLINING.
THE GLOBAL GRID PROVIDES
SUPPORT TAILORED
TO THE OPERATION AT HAND.
BY REMOVING THE
"ONE-SIZE-FITS-ALL" APPROACH,
OUR SYSTEM ALLOWS YOU TO EXPAND
WITHOUT INCREASING COST.
HEKMATYAR GLOBAL GRID
HAS LOW OVERHEAD.
NO LONGER WILL YOU NEED TO
WORRY ABOUT LAUNCHING
YOUR OWN SATELLITES,
OR MAINTAINING
YOUR OWN TRANSPORT FLEETS.
EVEN COUNTRIES WITH STRONG
LOGISTIC NETWORKS
CAN SAVE TIME AND MONEY BY USING
THE GRID FOR FORCE PROJECTIONS.
THE WORD "LOGISTICS" HAS
ITS ROOTS IN ANCIENT GREEK.
IT LITERALLY MEANS,
"AN EXPERT AT MATH."
MODERN MILITARY LOGISTICS
TRULY EXIST IN A WORLD
OF NUMBERS AND APPLIED MATH,
AND THE PEOPLE WHO EXCEL
AT THOSE THINGS ARE
IN THE PRIVATE SECTOR,
NOT THE MILITARY.
IF WARS ARE TO BE MOSTLY
PRIVATIZED,
LET THE PRIVATE SECTOR
DO WHAT IT DOES BEST--
COST-SAVINGS AND EFFICIENCY.
WHEN IT COMES TO MAKING MONEY,
GOVERNMENTS DON'T STAND A CHANCE
NEXT TO BUSINESSMEN LIKE ME.
- HUH?  HMM.
VERY INTERESTING PRESENTATION.
- DAMN IT, HINOKI.
WE GOTTA TEACH THAT BASTARD
THAT THE MILITARY CAN
STILL GET THINGS DONE.
- I THINK IT'S BEST TO WAIT AND
SEE HOW THIS PLAYS OUT, GENERAL.
DON'T FORGET, YOU STILL HAVE
THE POWER TO STRIKE
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
- CONTROLLING ALL WAR?
WHAT A FRAUD.
HE SOUNDS LIKE THE CRACKPOT
VILLAIN OUT OF SOME OLD
TIN-TIN COMIC STRIP.
- YEAH, THAT'S KASPER.
- AH, THE BOY SOLDIER SPEAKS.
SO IS THIS KASPER MAN
A FRIEND OF YOURS?
- NOT REALLY.
- HIS COMPANY JUST MADE
A VERY BIG ANNOUNCEMENT.
THIS IS LIVE FOOTAGE
OF THE PRESENTATION.
- HUH,
BUT IF IT WAS SO IMPORTANT
WHY WASN'T KOKO THERE WITH HIM?
SHE DIDN'T EVEN WATCH
THE BROADCAST.
- SO, KOKO, I MUST SAY,
I REMAIN VERY CURIOUS TO SEE
WHAT IT IS YOU'RE PLOTTING.
CAN I PLEASE BE A PART OF IT?
I'LL PAY.  NAME YOUR PRICE.
MONEY IS NO OBJECT.
- I BEG YOUR PARDON,
MS. TOROHOVSKY
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HCLI JUST ANNOUNCED THEIR
NEW LOGISTICS PACKAGE,
THE HEKMATYAR GLOBAL GRID,
WHICH WILL REVOLUTIONIZE
HOW ARMIES ARE SUPPLIED
AND HOW WARS ARE FOUGHT AND WON.
- THAT'S NOT WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT, KOKO.
FORGIVE ME.  I WAS TOO FORWARD
SPRINGING ALL THIS ON YOU.
I'LL GIVE IT A REST FOR TODAY,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
I'M GIVING UP ON THIS.
IF YOU FIND YOU NEED ME
FOR YOUR PROJECT, PLEASE CALL.
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE REFERRING TO.
- DASVIDANIYA FOR NOW.
THANK YOU FOR
YOUR BUSINESS, KOKO.
I'M SURE I'LL BE SEEING
YOU AGAIN SOON.
- THERE I WAS,
TRAVELING WITH AN ARMS DEALER.
LOOKING BACK,
I REALIZE I DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND KOKO AT ALL.
- Koko:
JONAH, LET'S TAKE A WALK.
OH, MAN, IT FEELS LIKE FALL IS
FINALLY STARTING TO SET IN.
- MM-HMM.
SHE WAS ALWAYS SO CLOSE TO ME,
YET IMPOSSIBLE TO REACH.
THAT WAS THE WOMAN
NAMED KOKO HEKMATYAR.
- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS OH, NO ♪
♪ OH, NO, NO, NO, NO... ♪
- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS
LOCO, I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪