- NO MATTER YOUR REASONS,
KOKO, YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
- JUST SO YOU KNOW, JONAH,
ENDING MY LIFE HERE WILL DO
NOTHING TO STOP JORMUNGAND.
DO YOU REALLY THINK
I WOULD DANGLE MY PLAN
IN SUCH A PRECARIOUS POSITION
THAT IT COULD
BE BROUGHT CRASHING DOWN
WITH THE MERE PULL
OF A TRIGGER?
THE FACT THAT I'M TELLING YOU
ANYTHING AT ALL ABOUT THIS
MEANS THAT NO MATTER
WHAT HAPPENS TO ME
FROM THIS MOMENT ON,
JORMUNGAND WILL BE EXECUTED
AND THE NEW WORLD WILL DAWN.
- YOU KNOW THIS ISN'T RIGHT!
- WHY NOT?
IF IT'S ABOUT THOSE 700,000
FALLING FROM THE SKY,
THEY'RE COLLATERAL DAMAGE.
YOU HONESTLY BELIEVE
THAT THIS WORLD IS PERFECT
AND DOESN'T NEED CHANGING?
GRANTED, THE CHANGE
REQUIRED IS RADICAL
AND, YES, MAYBE A BIT
RUTHLESS EVEN.
YOU TOLD ME
YOU STILL LOVE THE WORLD,
EVEN THOUGH
IT MAY HATE YOU.
THINK ABOUT
HOW NAIVE THAT SOUNDS.
"OH, IF EVERY
SINGLE PERSON ON EARTH
JUST TRIED TO BE
A LITTLE BIT NICER,
WHAT A WONDERFUL WORLD
IT WOULD BE."
( chuckles ) IT DOESN'T
WORK THAT WAY. SO SORRY.
I'VE WALKED THROUGH
MANY BATTLEFIELDS
AND IF THINGS CONTINUE
AS THEY ARE,
MY GUT TELLS ME
A MASSIVE WAR WILL BREAK OUT
WITHIN THE NEXT 10 YEARS.
THIS NEW WAR WON'T BE OVER OIL,
BUT OVER WATER.
IN SOME PLACES,
IT'S ALREADY BEGUN.
HUMANS CANNOT SURVIVE
WITHOUT CLEAN DRINKING WATER.
THEY WILL FIGHT
BECAUSE THEIR LIVES
WILL LITERALLY
DEPEND ON IT.
THE FIRST WORLD WAR CLAIMED
THE LIVES OF 40 MILLION PEOPLE.
WORLD WAR II WIPED
ANOTHER 66 MILLION
OFF THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
HOW MANY DO YOU THINK
WOULD DIE IN A THIRD?
- THIS WORLD HATES
ALL OF US, JONAH,
AND I HATE IT RIGHT BACK.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- EVERYWHERE I GO,
I ENCOUNTER NOTHING BUT WAR.
I HATE THE SIGHT OF BODIES PILED
UP ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
I HATE WEAPONS.
JUST REMEMBERING THE SENSATION
OF SOMEONE POINTING
ONE OF THOSE VILE TOOLS AT ME
GIVES ME A MIGRAINE.
I HATE SOLDIERS,
ESPECIALLY THE ONES
WHO SHUT OFF THEIR BRAINS
AND BLINDLY FOLLOW ORDERS.
THEY REEK WORSE THAN
THE BLOATED CORPSES
THEY LEAVE IN THEIR WAKE.
A PARENT IS WROUGHT
WITH GRIEF OVER LOSING
THEIR CHILD TO WAR,
SO WHAT DO THEY DO?
POP OUT ANOTHER AND VOW,
"I'LL TURN THIS BOY
INTO A SOLDIER."
CAN YOU IMAGINE
ANYTHING MORE IDIOTIC?
I HATE PEOPLE.
I FIND THE THOUGHT
THAT WE'RE FROM THE
SAME SPECIES DEPRESSING.
ONLY THOSE WHOSE DEATHS
HAVE BEEN DELIVERED
BY THE WEAPONS I'VE SOLD
HAVE EARNED MY PITY AND REMORSE.
I HATE
THAT I'M AN ARMS DEALER--
I COULDN'T ESCAPE
THAT FATE--
BUT IT SEEMS
I HAD A KNACK FOR IT,
AND THE CASH JUST POURED IN.
AND THEN ONE DAY IT HIT ME!
I COULD USE ALL THIS BLOOD
MONEY TO FOSTER PEACE.
THE ONLY WAY THE SOULS
OF THOSE KILLED
BY MY GUNS WILL EVER FORGIVE ME
IS IF I CAN TELL THEM,
"YOUR DEATHS WERE NOT IN VAIN."
THEY DROVE ME
TO BRING ABOUT WORLD PEACE!
THIS GODFORSAKEN PLANET'S
IN LUCK!
DESPITE MY BURNING HATRED
FOR IT,
I'VE DECIDED I'M GOING
TO HEAL THE FUCKING THING
RATHER THAN DESTROY IT!
AND WITH
NO MORE WEAPONS IN IT,
I MIGHT EVEN COME
TO LOVE THIS WORLD AGAIN.
BE AT MY SIDE
ON THIS, JONAH.
YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
I LOVE, JONAH.
AND I KNOW THAT
YOU'RE JUST LIKE ME.
WE SEE EYE TO EYE.
- ( hip-hop music playing )
- YOU KNOW
YOU HATE IT ALL, TOO--
WEAPONS, DEALERS, VIOLENCE--
BUT YOU'RE
A FIERCE BOY SOLDIER.
WHEN MY BROTHER
FIRST TOLD ME ABOUT YOU,
MY HEART DANCED
LIKE YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE.
YOU WERE MY...
- Both: LIMITER.
- NO.
- I'M WORRIED HE'S GOING TO
TURN YOU INTO A BIG SOFTIE.
- ( humphs )
- Koko's voice: THAT MAY BE
CLOSER TO THE TRUTH.
- IN EXCHANGE
FOR THE USE OF YOUR TALENTS
TO GUARD MY LIFE AND SAFETY,
I'M OFFERING YOU
A FRONT-ROW SEAT
TO HISTORY IN THE MAKING.
YOU'LL WITNESS THE MOMENT
I DESTROY THE SYSTEM THAT'S
TAKEN SO MUCH FROM YOU--
THE DAY WE ACHIEVE
WORLD PEACE.
COME, JONAH.
LIVE TOGETHER WITH ME
IN OUR NEW WORLD.
- ( sighs )
- UHH...
- GOODBYE, KOKO.
- OH, JONAH.
NO, COME BACK!  WAIT!
WHY CAN'T YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M DOING?
DON'T LEAVE ME!
- Jonah's voice:
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE
I'M NOT SMART,
BUT I CAN'T REALLY
GIVE HER AN ANSWER.
IS KOKO RIGHT?
IS SHE WRONG?
I KNOW I DON'T LIKE IT, BUT I
DON'T KNOW WHY I DON'T LIKE IT.
SO MY ONLY CHOICE...
IS TO RUN AWAY.
- ( Kasper chuckles )
A BIT CHILLY
TO BE TAKING A DIP IN
THE OCEAN, JONAH.
MY, WHAT A HAPPY COINCIDENCE,
MEETING YOU HERE.  YEAH?
- COINCIDENCE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE, KASPER?
- WELL, IT'S NOT
LIKE I WAS SPYING
ON YOUR
SQUAD OR ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST THAT MY INTUITION
IS USUALLY SPOT-ON,
AND IT TOLD ME
THAT IT WAS ABOUT TIME
FOR SOMEONE
TO ABANDON KOKO'S UNIT.
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
- CAN'T SAY.
- YOU ABOUT READY TO
GET OUT OF HERE?
- YEAH.
- Kasper: ALL RIGHT THEN.
- ( beeping )
- HOP IN.
- ( shudders )
( gasps ) WHAT?
- WILL YOU LOOK AT THAT?
ALL THIS TIME
I HAD YOU PEGGED
AS FULLY LACKING
IN THE EMOTION DEPARTMENT,
BUT YOU'VE GOT A WHOLE RANGE
OF EXPRESSIONS GOING ON.
OF COURSE, MOST OF 'EM
ARE IN THE RANGE OF SAD.
- BETWEEN THAT AND A
MAN WHO ALWAYS SMILES
FOR NO REASON,
I'D TAKE THIS DISPLAY
OF SORROW ANY DAY.
- ( laughs )
QUITE THE LADIES' MAN, JONAH.
BUT IF LEAVING
UPSETS YOU THIS MUCH,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO BACK?
I IMAGINE YOU STILL CAN.
- NO, I CAN'T.
- SO TELL ME,
MR. FORMER-CHILD-SOLDIER
- WHO-POSSESSES-
UNCANNY-FIGHTING-SKILL-
DESPITE-HATING-WAR,
WHERE DO YOU PLAN
ON GOING FROM HERE?
- YOU HAD TO DECIDE WHICH WAS
THE BETTER COURSE--
KILLING ME OR USING ME.
- KASPER SIR,
IF THERE IS ANY WAY,
CAN I PLEASE COME WORK FOR YOU?
- YEAH... YOU DON'T HAVE
TO BOW TO ME, JONAH.
WHEN YOU GOT
ALL QUIET BACK THERE,
I KNEW EXACTLY WHAT WAS
RUNNING THROUGH YOUR HEAD.
YOU TRULY ARE A KIND
YOUNG MAN, AREN'T YOU?
TO THE POINT
IT ALMOST WORRIES ME.
AND DROP THAT "SIR" CRAPOLA.
YOU AND I ARE
EQUALS HERE, OKAY?
ANYWAY, SURE, I'LL HIRE YOU.
WELCOME ABOARD.
- GLAD YOU'RE HERE, MISHKA.
- Men: YEAH!
- Kaspar: EDGAR, ALAN AND POE
ARE SUPER LAID BACK,
BUT CHEQUITA'S STRICT AS HELL,
SO WATCH YOURSELF.
- HEY, WHY ARE YOU MAKING
ME OUT TO BE THE BAD GUY?
- Jonah: UM, THANKS.
- Miami: I SEE.
SO JONAH LEFT YOU, HUH?
THAT SUCKS,
BUT DIDN'T YOU PREDICT
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
WOULD HAPPEN WITH HIM?
IT WAS INEVITABLE, REALLY.
JUST A MATTER OF TIME.
IT'S LIKE A RITE OF PASSAGE.
I MEAN, THIS IS A LOT
FOR A KID HIS AGE TO PROCESS.
AT LEAST ALL THE GROWNUPS
DECIDED TO STICK WITH YOU.
THE BOY JUST NEEDS
SOME TIME
TO THINK THINGS
OVER. YOU'LL SEE.
OKAY, NOW GO AND WIPE
THAT GLOOMY LOOK OFF YOUR FACE.
- I DO NOT LOOK GLOOMY.
- SO ANY IDEA
WHERE YOUNG JONAH WENT?
- TURNS OUT
MY BROTHER PICKED HIM UP.
I JUST HEARD THAT PART.
KASPER KNOWS
YOU'RE IN SOUTH AFRICA?
- ( sighs )
YOU KNOW HOW HE WORKS.
BETWEEN THE NOSEY
NELLIES AT H.Q.
RAISING SUSPICIONS
ABOUT MY ACTIVITIES
AND HIS GUT FEELING THAT
SOMEONE WAS ON THE VERGE
OF DITCHING MY TEAM...
- HUH?
- ...HE TOOK A CHANCE
AND CAME OUT HERE
JUST TO CHECK THINGS OUT.
- HMM. LIKE ME, YOU'LL
BOTH TRAVEL AROUND
THE WORLD ON A WHIM.
NOT TO SOUND RUDE,
BUT I DOUBT JONAH
WILL BE ABLE TO STAND
KASPER FOR VERY LONG.
- ( chuckles )
- IN FACT, I'M SURE.
JONAH WILL FIND
HIS OWN ANSWERS SOON.
AND THEN HE WILL MAKE
HIS WAY BACK TO YOU.
THAT ONE'S A SMART KID,
EVEN IF, FROM WHAT I HEAR,
HE TOTALLY SUCKS AT SCHOOLWORK.
- YEAH, TRUE.
HE IS PRETTY SMART, ISN'T HE?
AND I THINK THE WAY HE'S
SO TERRIBLE AT HIS STUDIES
IS ADORBS.
- ( laughs )
OH, SPEAKING OF TERRIBLE,
I GOTTA TALK TO YOU ABOUT...
( British accent )
DR. LEILA FAIZA.
( normal voice )
YOU KNOW, CHATTY RABBIT'S FOOT?
SHE'S IMPRESSIVE,
BUT WHEN I FIRST MET HER,
SHE DIDN'T EVEN
SAY HELLO! JUST...
- WHERE DO YOU KEEP
THE QUANTUM COMPUTER?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S RIGHT HERE IN FRONT
OF YOUR FREAKING FACE.
YOUR JOB IS
TO SHRINK IT ALL DOWN
SO IT FITS COMFORTABLY INSIDE
A 10-FOOT CONTAINER.
SHE'S THE EXACT
OPPOSITE OF JONAH--
BOOK SMART, BUT NOT A LICK
OF COMMON SENSE IN HER HEAD.
I CAN STILL USE HER,
GONNA TAKE SOME EXTRA
TRAINING, THOUGH.
- SHE KIND OF REMINDS ME
OF YOU IN SOME WAYS, MINAMI.
- OH PLEASE,
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
REMINDS YOU OF ME.
SO WHAT WILL YOU DO NOW?
- I'M GONNA CONTINUE
MY JOB AS AN ARMS DEALER,
THOUGH I EXPECT
I'LL BE CHECKING IN WITH YOU
HERE A BIT MORE FREQUENTLY.
- REALLY? IN THAT CASE,
YOU SHOULD COME TAKE A DIP
IN THE HOT SPRING TO RELAX.
- YEAH?  OKAY.
I'LL INVITE THE OTHER GIRLS TOO.
- GREAT IDEA!
VALMET IS
SUCH SWEET EYE CANDY!
- UH...
- AND THAT BABS HAS
A PRETTY NICE SET
OF MELONS ON HER, TOO.
- FOR REAL?
- Jonah's voice:
ALL WE EVER SEE ANYMORE
IS WAR AND CARNAGE.
I GUESS FIGHTING IS
THE ONLY THING
I'M ANY GOOD AT, KOKO.
- Koko: WHAT THE HELL
IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE?
YOU CAN'T JUST
SEND ME SOME RANDOM CHART
AND EXPECT ME TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT ALL MEANS.
- Miami:
JEEZ, DID YOU EVEN LOOK AT IT?
IT'S THE RECORD
OF A COUPLE OF GUYS
WHO HAVE BEEN
THOROUGHLY COMBING OVER
YOUR BANK ACCOUNTS.
THERE ARE TWO IN PARTICULAR
WHO HAVE BEEN GETTING CLOSE
TO THE CORE OF YOUR FINANCES.
FIRST ONE'S SCARECROW,
A C.I.A. OPERATIVE FROM LONDON.
- AH.
- THE OTHER'S TORY PLAME
OF THE S.C.S., G2.
HE ACCESSED YOUR ACCOUNT
FROM BOTH BELTSVILLE
AND FORT MEADE.
- HUH?
- ANY IDEA WHO THIS PLAME IS?
- I KEEP TELLING YOU
I CAN'T KEEP TRACK
OF EVERYONE I'VE PISSED OFF
OVER THE YEARS.
THEN AGAIN, THE AMOUNT OF
EFFORT HE'S PUT INTO THIS
MIGHT MEAN
HE'S A SPECIAL CASE.
THE N.S.A. IS PRIMARILY COMPOSED
OF HIGHLY-SKILLED TECHIES.
THE SPECIAL COLLECTION
SERVICE IS THE ONLY DIVISION
WITH ACTIVE SPIES.
SINCE THE N.S.A. DOESN'T HAVE
A UNIT OF IT'S OWN,
IT HAS TO PARTNER
WITH THE C.I.A.
WHEN CARRYING OUT
SECRET OPERATIONS.
- EH, YOU KNOW I DON'T CARE
ABOUT STUFF LIKE THAT.
- ( gasps )
- FIGURE IT OUT?
- UPTIGHT FOUR-EYED DOUCHEBAG--
FROM THE RABBIT'S FOOT JOB.
THAT MUST BE WHO PLAME IS.
SOMEBODY ORDERED
A TEAM OF NAVY SEALS
TO COME AFTER US.
IT DIDN'T WORK OUT SO WELL.
- Koko's voice:
I BET YOU'RE IN A TIGHT SPOT
AFTER LETTING SUCH
A BIG FISH GET AWAY,
AREN'T YOU, MR. PLAME?
SEEMS YOU CAN'T COMPREHEND
JORMUNGAND'S MAGIC.
BUT IF YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND IT,
HOW WILL YOU RESPOND TO IT?
- MINAMI, SEE IF YOU CAN CONNECT
THIS PLAME GUY TO GEORGE BLACK,
C.I.A. CLANDESTINE SERVICE.
HE'S THE BRANCH CHIEF
OF THEIR EUROPEAN OFFICE.
- Minami: OKEDOKE.
- HMM.  MMM.
WHOA!  THAT'S SOME
DAMN GOOD CHOCOLATE.
- Tojo:
YEAH?  WHAT KIND IS IT?
- SO WHAT DOES
EVERYBODY THINK ABOUT IT?
THE BOSS LADY'S PLAN?
- JEEZ, LUTZ, YOU'RE LIKE
A BROKEN RECORD.
ASK US AGAIN WHY DON'T YA?
- WELL, I'M NOT JUST ASKING.
I'VE ACTUALLY GOT
SOME THOUGHTS OF MY OWN
I'D LIKE
TO CONTRIBUTE THIS TIME.
- YEAH?  THEN BY ALL MEANS,
PLEASE ENLIGHTEN US.
- OKAY, SO RECENTLY
IT STARTED SEEMING TO ME
LIKE THE LITTLE LADY WAS GROWING
MORE AND MORE AGGRESSIVE--
YOU KNOW,
ABDUCTIONS AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
REMEMBER?
- I REMEMBER YOU WHINING
ABOUT IT ALL THE DAMN TIME.
- Lutz:
I ASKED VALMET HER OPINION,
BUT HER ANSWER
DIDN'T QUITE HELP.
HOWEVER, WHEN I HEARD
THE LITTLE LADY
EXPLAIN HER PLAN,
EVERYTHING FINALLY
CAME TOGETHER
AND MADE A WHOLE
SHIT-TON MORE SENSE.
- ( door opens )
- I MEAN,
IT ALL MADE PERFECT SENSE.
- Tojo:
WHY THE SUDDEN CHOIRBOY ACT?
- KOKO'S ON A PHONE CALL.
PLEASE DON'T STOP
BECAUSE OF ME.
- OKAY, SO I'VE DECIDED
I'M GONNA THROW
MY FULL SUPPORT BEHIND KOKO,
BUT I WAS CURIOUS
HOW YOU GUYS FELT.
- SHE'S GOT MY BACKING.
I THINK IT'D BE COOL
TO BE ONE OF THE LAST
SOLDIERS ON EARTH.
PLUS I'D KINDA LIKE TO LIVE
IN A WORLD WITHOUT WEAPONS.
- HUH?  ME?
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WORKING FOR KOKO
I'VE COME
TO REALIZE SOMETHING--
IT TURNS OUT I HAVE
THE SPIRIT OF A TRUE ARTIST.
I WANT TO KEEP SERVING
KOKO ALL THE WAY,
UNTIL SHE NO LONGER REQUIRES
MY PARTICULAR SET OF SKILLS.
- YEAH, I SECOND EVERYTHING
WILEE JUST SAID.
DO I BACK HER PLAN?
WHO CARES?
I BACK HER.
- AS FOR ME,
WELL, HEY,
BUSINESS IS BUSINESS.
SO YEAH, MY FEELINGS
HAVEN'T CHANGED.
BUT THEN THERE'S THE KID.
I CAN'T QUITE
WRAP MY HEAD AROUND
HOW JONAH COULD JUST
UP AND LEAVE THE WAY HE DID.
I WONDER WHAT LEHM'S TAKE
IS ON ALL OF THIS.
- WELL, I THINK--
- Men: YES, VALMET,
WE ALL KNOW WHAT YOU THINK.
- ( cellphone buzzes, beeps )
- Koko: BOOK MAN!
LONG TIME, NO SPEAK.
YOU KNOW WHO THIS IS, RIGHT?
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
I KNOW, I KNOW, YOU'RE SHOCKED.
I HAVE SOME WORK
TO GET TO IN A MINUTE,
SO I WON'T HESITATE
TO HANG UP ON YOU
IF YOU GIVE ME ANY TROUBLE.
THOUGH I MUST SAY YOU HAVE
EVEN LESS TIME THAN I DO.
SOMEONE OUT THERE
HAS BEEN CONNECTING THE DOTS
BETWEEN YOUR
"OPERATION UNDERSHAFT"
AND ME AND A LITTLE HICCUP
IN A RECENT MISSION INVOLVING
SOME VERY SPECIAL SOLDIERS.
- ( laughs )
YOU REALIZE YOU JUST IMPLIED
YOU WERE ENTWINED
IN AN ASSAULT AGAINST MY NATION.
- LISTEN OR DON'T,
IT'S UP TO YOU.
BUT AT THIS RATE, BOOK MAN,
YOU'LL BE SWEATING IT
ON A WITNESS STAND
WITHIN THE WEEK.
IF YOU'D LIKE TO DISCUSS
THIS FURTHER AND IN PERSON,
GET YOUR ASS TO DULLES
AND ONTO THE FLIGHT
I'VE ARRANGED.
YOU SHOULD ARRIVE
IN NORTH AFRICA BY THIS EVENING.
( laughs )
GOOD LUCK.
- ( hangs up )
- WHAT'S HER ANGLE?
WHATEVER IT IS,
I HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO GO.
- DAMN, THAT TOOK
WAY TOO FREAKING LONG.
I CAN'T KEEP
THE COLONEL WAITING.
- HAVE A GOOD DAY, TORY.
- THANKS, HONEY. YOU TOO.
- THINK YOU'LL BE HOME
AT A REASONABLE HOUR?
- YEAH, I DON'T HAVE
ANY MEETINGS SCHEDULED
AND I'M NOT INVOLVED
IN ANY MAJOR OPERATIONS, SO--
- ( coos )
- OH, SEE YOU SOON.
- ( cellphone rings, beeps )
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- DID YOU NEED
TO TAKE THAT CALL,
MISS HEKMATYAR?
PLEASE DON'T
IGNORE IT ON MY BEHALF.
- NO BIG DEAL.
REALLY, IT CAN WAIT.
BESIDES, I CAN'T THINK
OF ANYTHING IN THE WORLD
MORE IMPORTANT RIGHT NOW
THAN MY CONVERSATION
WITH YOU, COLONEL.
- ( laughs ) GOODNESS,
YOU'RE QUITE THE CHARMER.
- Man: CAPTAIN, WE JUST GOT
NEW ORDERS FROM H.Q.
- Captain: REALLY?
FROM OUR GLORIOUS LEADER?
WELL, DON'T JUST STAND THERE,
READ IT.
- "MY BROTHERS,
A VILE UNWELCOME AMERICAN SPY
TRESPASSES
ON OUR SACRED LAND.
YOU MUST CAPTURE THIS DEVIL
AND ENGRAVE OUR RIGHTEOUS ANGER
INTO HIS ODIOUS BODY.
I EXPECT YOUR GROUP,
SHIVERING IN A NEW DAWN,
TO ACT SWIFTLY AND EFFICIENTLY."
- GET EVERYONE READY!
- Man #2:
THIS IS A RESCUE MISSION
FOR A TOP-VALUE ASSET!
A HIGH-RANKING MEMBER
OF THE C.I.A.
HAS BEEN STRANDED
IN A NORTH AFRICAN WAR ZONE.
YOU WILL INFILTRATE VIA HELO!
GET HIM BACK HERE ASAP!
IF YOU ENCOUNTER
ARMED HOSTILES,
YOU HAVE
PERMISSION TO OPEN FIRE!
- Men: SIR, YES SIR!
- ( chuckles )
- ( trucks approaching )
- Black: OH CRAP.
SHE SET ME UP.
- ( tires screech )
- ( grunts )
- ( gunshot )
- ( tires screech )
- ( guns firing )
- SHIT!  SNIPERS!
WHO THE FUCK?
WERE WE SET UP?
- ( whimpers )
LIGHT 'EM UP!
- ( guns cocking )
- THIS MAKES NO SENSE!
- HEY, ARE YOU GEORGE BLACK?
U.S. MARINE CORPS.
- HUH?  UH, YEAH.
- Black's voice: AN ENTIRE
PLATOON SENT TO RESCUE JUST ME?
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
COME ON, PULL IT TOGETHER
AND THINK THIS THROUGH.
THE TIMING OF IT ALL
IS PRETTY SUSPICIOUS,
A LOCAL ARMED MILITIA
JUST HAPPENS TO SHOW UP,
GUNS A'BLAZING,
AS SOON AS I ARRIVE?
AND THEN THE MARINES
COME IN TO SAVE MY HIDE
JUST IN THE NICK OF TIME?
IT FEELS ALMOST TOO PERFECT,
LIKE IT WAS CHOREOGRAPHED.
- SIR, THE PACKAGE IS SECURE.
SIR, OPERATION UNDERSHAFT
WILL PROCEED AS PLANNED.
- THAT'S YOUR
MISSION'S CODENAME?
- YES, THAT IS CORRECT.
THIS MISSION HAS BEEN GIVEN
THE DESIGNATION
"OPERATION UNDERSHAFT," SIR.
- ( laughing )
- DID I SAY SOMETHING
TO AMUSE YOU, SIR?
BECAUSE YOU KNOW
WHAT I FIND PRETTY AMUSING?
WEARING A SUIT IN A WAR ZONE.
- NO, I JUST REALIZED
I'D BEEN HAD
BY A GIRL HALF MY AGE.
WHEN YOU'RE IN THIS GAME
AS LONG AS ME,
IT'S BOUND
TO HAPPEN EVENTUALLY.
- FOR REAL?
- Black's voice: IF SHE USED
THAT QUANTUM COMPUTER
OR WHATEVER SHE'S GOT,
IT'D BE A PIECE OF CAKE
FOR HER TO ISSUE
OPERATION ORDERS
OR FORGE EMAILS
FROM A TERRORIST NETWORK.
SHE PROBABLY KNOWS EXACTLY
WHAT I'M DOING RIGHT NOW.
KOKO HEKMATYAR HAS MORPHED
INTO THE GODDESS OF INFORMATION.
SHE SKIPPED RIGHT PAST
THE MONSTER STAGE
AND BECAME THE MOST POWERFUL
PERSON ON THE PLANET.
SO WHY DOESN'T
SHE JUST CONQUER IT?
- Koko:
HERE'S A HYPOTHETICAL.
A UTOPIA APPEARS.
- OF COURSE! SHE ACTUALLY
AIMS TO CREATE A NEW WORLD.
GOD HELP ME,
I'D LIKE TO SEE IT.
SHE EXPECTED ME
TO FEEL THIS WAY.
SHE SOMEHOW KNEW
THAT I'D BE ON HER SIDE,
DESPITE MY WORKING
FOR THE C.I.A.
THE LITTLE LADY HAD ME
FIGURED OUT A LONG TIME AGO.
THAT'S WHY SHE DIDN'T
HAVE ME KILLED BACK THERE.
SHE THINKS SHE CAN USE ME.
WELL, THAT'S FINE.
GO AHEAD AND USE ME.
COME TO THINK OF IT,
I CAN'T BE THE ONLY ONE
SHE ENSNARED IN THIS TRAP.
WHATEVER POOR SAP
SHE SET UP TO TAKE THE FALL
FOR ORDERING THAT HIT ON ME
IS GONNA BE IN IT DEEP.
( humphs )
I DON'T ENVY HIM.
- ( door opens )
- ( gasps )
- Man:
N.S.A. POLICE.
G2 SECTION CHIEF TORY PLAME,
SPECIAL COLLECTIONS,
YOU ARE UNDER ARREST
FOR SUSPICION OF VIOLATING
THE FOREIGN INTELLIGENCE
SURVEILLANCE ACT.
WE NEED YOU TO COME WITH US.
- UH, WHAT?
- PLAME, THESE GENTLEMEN
ARE SAYING YOU CONTRACTED
AN ARMED MILITIA
IN NORTH AFRICA TO CARRY OUT
THE ASSASSINATION
OF A HIGH-LEVEL C.I.A. OFFICIAL.
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
- THAT'S A WRAP.
- MY MY, KOKO.
YOU ARE SIMPLY HORRIBLE,
AREN'T YOU?
- OH, I'LL LET PLAME
WRIGGLE FREE SOON ENOUGH.
- ( chuckles )
- WHAT CAN I SAY? I'M A BAD GUY.
THOUGH THESE DAYS,
THERE'S ALL KINDS
OF BAD GUYS IN THE WORLD.
- AND WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- I'M JUST WONDERING WHICH KIND
YOU-KNOW-WHO WILL CHOOSE
IN THE END.
- Kasper:
MAN, WHAT A PAIN IN THE ASS,
BUT THANK GOD
THOSE SPARKS FINALLY IGNITED.
IT MADE SELLING
ALL THOSE CUTTING-EDGE WEAPONS
TO EVERYONE WORTH MY WHILE.
AND IF BOTH ARMIES END UP
WIPING EACH OTHER OUT,
IT GIVES ME THE OPENING
TO BUILD THAT PIPELINE.
- Jonah's voice: OUR PATH IS
SO OVERRUN WITH WEAPONS
THAT SOMETIMES I WONDER
IF THE WHOLE WORLD
IS MADE UP OF NOTHING
BUT IRON AND GUNPOWDER.
AS I CLENCHED THAT TOOL,
DESIGNED FOR THE SOLE PURPOSE
OF TAKING LIVES...
I'D FORGOTTEN HOW MUCH
I USED TO HATE WEAPONS.
- JONAH, LET'S GO.
- Jonah's voice:
HERE I AM...
TRAVELING WITH
ANOTHER ARMS DEALER.
- ( theme music playing )
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪