- ( gunfire )
- Lehm: YO, WILEE!
LOOKING FOR A WILEE COYOTE.
ANYBODY SEEN A WILEE COYOTE?
MAJORED IN ARCHITECTURE
AT UVA?
SAPPER IN THE 20th ENGINEER
BRIGADE, 18th AIRBORNE CORPS.
WHERE THE FUCK IS
LIEUTENANT WILLIAM NELSON?
- I'M WILLIAM NELSON.
YES, SIR.
- AH-HA, SO YOU DO EXIST.
CAPTAIN LEHMBRICK,
FIRST SPECIAL FORCES
OPERATIONAL DETACHMENT, DELTA.
MAYBE YOU'VE HEARD OF US.
IT'S GOOD TO MEET YOU.
- SIR, IT'S AN HONOR
TO MEET YOU.
- I'M GONNA PUT YOUR PARTICULAR
SKILL SET TO WORK, CAVALIER.
- DELTA FORCE.
WHAT COULD THEY POSSIBLY WANT
WITH ME?
IF YOU GUYS ARE DELTA FORCE,
DOES THAT MEAN WE'RE GOING
ON A SCUD HUNT?  ARE WE GONNA
BLOW UP SOME OF SADDAM'S TELS?
- Lehm: SOMEBODY'S GOT
A HARD-ON TO SEE SOME ACTION,
BUT THIS AIN'T THAT BIG A JOB.
NO NEED TO GET TOO WORKED UP.
THERE'LL BE FOUR OF US,
PLUS YOU.
WE'RE DEMOLISHING
A CHEMICAL WEAPONS PLANT.
ONE OF OUR SPY SATELLITES WAS
ABLE TO LOCATE THE PLANT
AT THE FOOT OF A MOUNTAIN
IN NORTHERN IRAQ.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO FLATTEN THE
PLACE WITHIN THE NEXT 40 HOURS.
WE GOT NO PICTURES OF THE INSIDE
OF THIS THING.
SO THAT'S WHERE YOU COME IN
WITH YOUR EXPERTISE
IN EXPLOSIVE DEMOLITION.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU TO LEVEL IT
WITH ONLY A LIMITED SUPPLY
OF FIREWORKS.
- SIR, THIS SOUNDS LIKE
A BIG JOB TO ME.
I'VE ONLY EVER WRITTEN A THESIS
ON STRUCTURAL DEMOLITION.
- WELL, YOU GOT EXPERIENCE AS
A COMBAT ENGINEER, DON'T YOU?
EASE UP, YOU'LL BE FINE.
- Echo: CAPTAIN,
IS THIS THE FAMOUS WILEE?
WILEE, THIS HERE IS
SERGEANT FIRST-CLASS ARKIN.
- GOOD TO MEET YOU, SOLDIER.
- AND BEHIND THE WHEEL'S
SERGEANT HOWE.
- S'UP, MAN?
- RIGHT, ALMOST FORGOT,
I'M LIEUTENANT ECKHART,
BUT YOU CAN CALL ME "ECHO."
- NICE TO MEET YOU.  NELSON.
- I TOLD ECKHART TO DROP THE
NICKNAME SO WE DON'T CONFUSE IT
FOR THE ICAO WORD FOR "E,"
BUT HE'S STUBBORN.
ALLOW ME TO FORMALLY INTRODUCE
LIEUTENANT WILEE NELSON,
OUR HASTY EXPLOSIVES FREAK.
BE GENTLE ON HIM, BOYS.
- ( all laughing )
- Echo: "CAPTAIN LEHMBRICK"
CAN BE A MOUTHFUL,
SO YOU CAN JUST CALL
HIM "LEHM."
"CAP'N" OR "OLD FART" WORK, TOO.
- I'M NOT THAT OLD A FART, AM I?
- ( laughs )
OH, WILEE, ALMOST FORGOT.
- YES, SIR.
- SORRY, BUT THIS IS ALL WE GOT
TO GO OFF OF.
- ( engine sputters )
- ( shouting )
- GUESSING THE PILLARS
WERE BUILT HERE.
- Echo: CHILL OUT, DUDE,
IT'S ALL GOOD.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF THE GUARDS.
GIVING YOU PLENTY OF TIME
TO PLANT YOUR EXPLOSIVES.
WAIT, BOTH YOUR PARENTS
AND YOUR GRANDPA
ARE ARCHITECTS?
THEN YOU WENT TO SCHOOL
TO STUDY ARCHITECTURE
JUST SO YOU COULD JOIN THE ARMY
AND BLOW BUILDINGS UP,
INSTEAD OF DESIGNING 'EM?
HOLY SHIT, DUDE.
YOU'RE EVEN CRAZIER THAN WE ARE.
- ( all laughing )
- Lehm: ALL RIGHT, LADIES, LET'S
START CLIMBING DOWN THIS ROCK.
- THEY'RE LIKE COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PEOPLE
THAN A MINUTE AGO.
SO THIS IS DELTA FORCE.
THESE GUYS ARE GOOD.
WHILE WE WERE JUST SHOOTING
THE SHIT UP THERE,
WHILE ECHO WAS DRAWING ME
INTO CONVERSATION,
WE REACHED THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS PLANT.
THEY'RE MACHINES.
- OH!
THEY'RE LIKE FREE-MOVING TURRETS
THAT HAVE BEEN PROGRAMMED ONLY
TO SEEK AND DESTROY THE ENEMY.
- ALL CLEAR.
- HE'S SO CALM.
HE MAKES IT SOUND LIKE THEY'RE
JUST CLEANING HOUSE.
- YOU CAN COME OUT, WILEE.
FOLLOW US.
- ( grunting )
NOT LIKE I HAVE A CHOICE HERE.
- WE WASTED MOST OF THE GUARDS,
BUT REINFORCEMENTS
WILL BE HERE SOON.
YOU'RE UP, CAVALIER.
WORK FASTER THAN
YOU'VE EVER WORKED BEFORE.
- YES, SIR!
I EXPECTED SOMETHING LIKE THIS,
BUT DAMN IT,
HOW MANY OF THESE STUPIDLY HUGE
SUPPORT PILLARS ARE IN HERE?
ALL FIVE OF US CARRIED
IN EXPLOSIVES,
BUT IT'S NOWHERE
NEAR ENOUGH.  UNLESS...
- FUCK.  WILEE!
- THAT IS SOME INTENSE
FOCUS YOU GOT THERE.
YOU ARE ONE CRAZY
DAMN COYOTE.
- ECHO, I NEED A HAND.
- YOU GOT IT.
WHAT'S UP?
- Wilee:
THIS SHOULD BE FAR ENOUGH.
PLUS, THAT'S ALL
THE DET CORD WE GOT.
- HIT IT.
- YES, SIR.
HOLY SHIT.
IT ACTUALLY WORKED.
- WHOA!  WE FLATTENED THAT
THING LIKE A DAMN PANCAKE.
AND HERE I THOUGHT
IT WAS GONNA BE MORE
OF A BIG KABOOM, YOU KNOW?
BUT THAT LOOKED SO CLEAN
AND PROFESSIONAL.
- IT WAS AWESOME.
- SHORT AS WE WERE ON EXPLOSIVES
IT WAS PRETTY DAMN CLEVER
TO RIG WHAT LITTLE WE HAD
TO THE 250-GAUGE CHEMICAL BOMBS
IN THERE.
I'D SAY THAT'S WORTHY
OF ADMIRATION.
- WINTER, 1991.
I HAD THE PRIVILEGE
OF WITNESSING FIRSTHAND A TEAM
OF ELITE SOLDIERS IN ACTION.
THEY WERE BOTH TERRIFYING
AND AWE-INSPIRING.
AND AFTER EARNING THEIR PRAISE,
I HAD ONLY ONE GOAL.
- ECHO.
- HUH?  WILEE.
FANCY SEEING YOU HERE IN
FAYETTE-NAM.  IT'S BEEN FOREVER.
SO I HEAR YOU'VE BEEN
KILLING IT IN YOUR OTC.
COME COP A SQUAT.
YOU ACED THE FINAL EXAM, HUH?
CONGRATULATIONS, I GUESS THAT
MAKES US COLLEAGUES NOW.
- THANKS, YEAH, I GUESS IT DOES.
MEET EXPLOSIVES EXPERT
WILEE COYOTE.
- OH, COOL, LIKE THE CARTOON?
- SO HOW'S CAPTAIN LEHM DOING?
- WELL, IT'S MAJOR LEHM
AND HE RETIRED.
- HUH?
- YOU WANNA SEE HIM?
I CAN GIVE YOU HIS CONTACT INFO.
- THAT'D BE COOL.
- WAIT A SEC.
DID YOU ALWAYS HAVE THOSE LINES
SHAVED ABOVE YOUR EARS?
- Woman: OOH, THAT'S HOT.
- THAT'S WHERE YOU GOT SHOT BACK
IN THE GULF WAR, RIGHT?
DON'T TELL ME,
THE HAIR WOULDN'T GROW BACK
SO YOU SHAVED THE OTHER SIDE
TO MATCH?
YOU'RE AS CRAZY
AS EVER, WILEE.
- ( all laughing )
- Wilee: SO I WENT TO FIND LEHM,
THE MAN I'D SO ADMIRED
AND THAT'S
WHEN I FIRST MET KOKO.
ENCHANTED BY HER CHARISMA,
I LEFT THE ARMY
TO JOIN HER, TOO.
- NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES
HE TELLS IT,
WILEE'S STORY IS ALWAYS A HIT.
- Jonah: GOOD STORY ABOUT
WHY WILEE SHAVES THOSE STREAKS.
- ( laughing )
- Koko: OH, JONAH.
IS THAT REALLY THE ONLY THING
YOU GOT OUT OF WILEE'S STORY?
- YOU HAVE MEN ON YOUR SQUAD
WHO SERVED IN THE GULF WAR?
- ABOUT 20 YEARS AGO,
THEY CAME HERE TO FIGHT,
BUT NOW THEY'VE RETURNED TO HELP
US BUILD A SCHOOL FOR CHILDREN.
I CANNOT TELL YOU HOW
MUCH THIS WARMS MY HEART.
- OH, NAZAL.  WE'RE NOT HERE
BECAUSE WE WANNA BE.
IT'S JUST BAD FOR MY IMAGE IF
ALL I EVER DO IS SELL WEAPONS,
SO THIS COSTLY PR STUNT IS
ABOUT REPAIRING MY REPUTATION,
NOT YOUR COUNTRY'S
CRUMBLING INFRASTRUCTURE.
- THAT IS ONE BLUNT WOMAN.
- I'VE GOT MY OWN GROUP
OF HIGHLY SKILLED
PERSONAL BODYGUARDS,
SO I DON'T NEED SOME LAME-ASS
BRITISH PMC LIKE EXCALIBUR,
OR AN INTERPRETER LIKE YOU,
FOR THAT MATTER.
I SPEAK ARABIC AS WELL
AS YOU DO.
- I'M SURE THAT'S TRUE,
MS. HEKMATYAR,
BUT PLEASE TEMPER
YOUR FRUSTRATION.
FOR A CONVOY OF TEN TRUCKS,
YOU NEED A MINIMUM OF 20 GUARDS
TO ENSURE SAFE PASSAGE.
THAT IS COMMON PRACTICE
AMONG ALL PMCs IN IRAQ.
SO YES, YOU DO NEED THEM.
AS TO MY NECESSITY,
IT SEEMS NO ONE
IN EXCALIBUR UNDERSTANDS ARABIC.
- DAMN, I WANNA SHOOT SOMETHING.
- HELL, YEAH, I GOT WAY
TOO MUCH PENT-UP ENERGY.
- NEVER MIND THAT.  YOU SEE
THE JUBBLIES ON THAT ONE BIRD?
BLEEDIN' MASSIVE.
- RIGHT?  CAN'T MISS 'EM.
I'D THROW MYSELF
ON THOSE GRENADES.
- JEEZ, THEY KNOW IT'S
AN OPEN CHANNEL, RIGHT?
FUCKING MORONS.
- KOKO, CAR APPROACHING
FAST FROM BEHIND.
IT MIGHT TRY TO PASS.
- COPY, JONAH.
WHOEVER'S IN BACK,
CHECK IT OUT.
- Tojo: AN OLD MAN BY HIMSELF.
SHOULDN'T GIVE US ANY TROUBLE.
- Mao: NOT SEEING ANY WEAPONS.
- HE'S HOSTILE.
LET'S TAKE HIM DOWN.
- OH!
- ( laughing )
- Lutz: WHAT THE FUCK?!
CEASE FIRE.  CEASE FIRE!
- IT'S TOO LATE NOW.
- ( tires screeching )
- WHOO!
DAMN, THAT FELT GOOD.
- Lehm:
THESE GUYS ARE INSANE.
- IF WE STOP THE CONVOY OVER
EVERY LITTLE BUMP IN THE ROAD,
IT'LL TAKE US DAYS
TO GET THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
KIND OF CAKEWALK
SUNDAY-IN-THE-PARK PLACES
YOU BEEN SELLING YOUR SHIT,
LADY, BUT THIS IS I-FUCKIN'-RAQ.
- I'M AWARE, BUT YOU DON'T NEED
TO WORRY ABOUT HOW LONG
IT'S GOING TO TAKE US
TO GET THERE,
BECAUSE I'M FIRING YOUR ASSES.
- HUH?
- WHAT, ARE YOUR EARS FULL
OF CRAP, TOO?
AND DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
LAYING SO MUCH AS
A FINGER ON MY WARES.
NOW GET THE HELL OUT
OF MY SIGHT,
YOU LIMEY THUGS!
SORRY ABOUT THAT, GUYS.
I WENT BARGAIN SHOPPING
FOR ESCORTS.
I DIDN'T KNOW THE PAY SCALE WAS
DIRECTLY RELATED TO THEIR IQ.
- ( laughing )
- BY THE WAY, I'VE ASKED
EXCALIBUR'S INTERPRETER NAZAL
TO STAY ON AND
DRIVE TRUCK SEVEN FOR US.
AND HE AIN'T CHEAP
BY ANY DEFINITION OF THE WORD.
- ( all laughs )
- I HAVE NEVER ENCOUNTERED A PMC
QUITE LIKE THIS ONE BEFORE.
- VALMET,
IT'S BEEN FOREVER
SINCE I'VE SEEN YOU DRIVE
A SEMI LIKE THIS.
YOU LOOK SO COOL.
- ( gasps ) DO YOU THINK SO?
DOES THIS MEAN
YOU'RE FALLING
EVEN DEEPER IN LOVE WITH ME
THEN BEFORE?
I WAS IN THE MECHANIZED
JAEGER SQUAD,
SO MY BODY STILL REMEMBERS HOW
TO DRIVE ALL KINDS
OF ARMORED CARS AND TRANSPORTS.
KOKO, YOU WANNA LEARN HOW?
I COULD GUIDE YOUR HANDS
AND FEET,
PUTTING THAT ON HOLD A MOMENT,
ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
- SURE ABOUT WHAT?
DITCHING EXCALIBUR?
- NO, WE'RE MUCH SAFER
WITHOUT THOSE SCUMBAGS.
WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT
IS KEEPING NAZAL WITH US.
OBVIOUSLY WE CAN USE HIS HELP,
SINCE WE'RE SHORT A DRIVER,
BUT THAT WHOLE, "I HAVE SOME
FREE TIME NOW THAT EXCALIBUR'S
BEEN DISMISSED SO I WANNA GO
HOME, WHICH JUST SO HAPPENS
TO BE NEAR YOUR DESTINATION SO I
MIGHT AS WELL LEND A HAND" THING
SOUNDS PRETTY SUSPICIOUS TO ME.
I BET THEY LEFT HIM BEHIND TO
REPORT OUR LOCATION.  HE'S A--
- DRINK UP,
IT'S IMPORTANT TO STAY HYDRATED.
- IT IS KIND OF SHADY THEY
DIDN'T PUT UP MUCH OF A FIGHT.
JUDGING BY PAST EXPERIENCE,
MACHO THUGS LIKE THAT
RARELY LEAVE JUST
'CAUSE YOU TELL 'EM TO.
HEY, GUYS, THESE GOODS AREN'T
EXACTLY WORTH MILLIONS,
SO FEEL FREE TO DITCH THE CONVOY
IF THEY COME BACK.
- KOKO, DO WE REALLY WANNA GET
STUCK OUT HERE IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE DESERT WITHOUT WHEELS?
- HMM GOOD POINT, MAO.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
IF THOSE CLOWNS FIRE SO MUCH AS
ONE SHOT, WE EXTERMINATE THEM.
- All: ROGER THAT.
- Valmet:
WAY TO ISSUE A BADASS ORDER.
- WOW, THESE PEOPLE ARE PRETTY
DAMN CRAZY THEMSELVES.
- IT'S A MATTER OF TIME BEFORE
THOSE GUYS RETURN AND ATTACK US.
- FUNNY.  I WAS JUST THINKING
THE SAME THING.
NOWADAYS JOKERS LIKE THEM
ARE EVERYWHERE.
I SWEAR, THE WAY WARS ARE
FOUGHT CHANGES OVERNIGHT.
JUST KEEPS GETTING NASTIER
AND NASTIER.
CRIPES, WHEN WE FOUGHT OUT
HERE ABOUT 20 YEARS AGO,
PEOPLE WERE SAYING,
"IT LOOKS LIKE A VIDEO GAME."
CUT TO TODAY AND YOU GOT
FUCKING BUSINESSMEN MIXED IN
WITH THE SQUADS OUT THERE
FIGHTING.
- YOU SAID YOU WERE HERE
20 YEARS AGO.
YOU MEAN IN THE GULF WAR, RIGHT?
- WELL, LOOK WHOSE MATH
IS GETTING BETTER.
- I HEARD WILEE TALKING EARLIER
ABOUT HOW MUCH HE ADMIRED YOU
AS A SOLDIER BACK THEN.
- IS THAT SO?
I ASSUME HE USED THE WORDS
"MAJESTIC" AND "DIVINE"?
- YEAH, NO,
HE DIDN'T GO THAT FAR.
- I MUST'VE MISSED THIS
WHILE I WAS MONITORING
EXCALIBUR'S CHANNEL.
WHAT'S GOING ON, WILEE?
TURN NOSTALGIC THE SECOND
WE TOUCHED DOWN IN IRAQ?
HE'S GETTING UP THERE
IN YEARS HIMSELF NOW.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING, JONAH?
WHILE IT'S A GIVEN THAT
I'M A SUPER SOLDIER,
WILEE'S A DAMN IMPRESSIVE
WARRIOR IN HIS OWN RIGHT.
IN FACT, I'D GO SO FAR AS TO SAY
HE'S DOWNRIGHT DANGEROUS.
- REALLY?
- LET'S PUT IT THIS WAY.
TWO MEMBERS OF OUR CREW HAVE
SPOTS ON THE FBI'S BLACKLIST,
THE BOSS LADY AND WILEE.
- HOLD ON A MINUTE.
THE AUTHORITIES CONSIDER HIM
JUST AS DANGEROUS AS KOKO?
- DAMN STRAIGHT.  LET ME TELL
YOU SOMETHING ABOUT WILEE.
THE REASON HE'S DRIVING
THE TRUCK UP AT THE FRONT,
IT'S 'CAUSE HE CAN
SNIFF OUT BOMBS.
COMES FROM HIS EXPERIENCE
AS A FORMER COMBAT ENGINEER.
NOT TO MENTION HE'S A CERTIFIED
EXPLOSIVES EXPERT
WHO'S BEEN ON TONS OF MISSIONS.
HE'S GOT A SIXTH SENSE
FOR KNOWING WHERE AN AMATEUR'S
PLANTED A BOMB.
EVER SINCE KOKO FIRST EMERGED
ON THE SCENE AS AN ARMS DEALER,
WE'VE HAD TO FEND OFF
BOMB THREATS.
WHEN YOUR DAD'S THE KING
OF INTERNATIONAL SHIPPING,
PEOPLE TEND TO TRY AND ABDUCT
OR KILL YOU ON A REGULAR BASIS.
YOU KNOW, "IF YOU DON'T WANNA
BE BLOWN TO SMITHEREENS,
GIVE US WHAT WE WANT."
WILEE MANAGED TO RENDER
ALL THOSE THREATS IDLE.
SEE, AFTER HANGING AROUND KOKO
LONG ENOUGH,
WILEE'S SKILLS GREW TO SURPASS
EVEN THE VERY
BEST BOMB-MAKERS OUT THERE.
HIS THING IS TO GIVE IT RIGHT
BACK TO THE WOULD-BE BOMBERS,
WHICH I BET CONFUSED
THE HELL OUT OF THE POLICE.
ALL THESE ASSASSINS
WHO WERE AFTER KOKO
STARTED BLOWING
THEMSELVES UP LEFT AN RIGHT.
WILEE WAS AN OBVIOUS SUSPECT,
BUT THEY WEREN'T HIS HANDIWORK.
AND THE ONLY PEOPLE
DYING WERE TERRORISTS.
THERE WAS THIS ONE TIME
IN TURKEY OR GREECE,
SOME GRIMY HOTEL PACKED
WITH ENOUGH EXPLOSIVES
TO BLOW IT SKY HIGH.
ARE WE GOOD?
- YEAH, PIECE OF CAKE.
- WHEN THE BOMB DIDN'T GO OFF,
THE CULPRIT WENT BACK INSIDE
TO SEE WHAT WAS WRONG.
- ( clicks )
- Lehm: THAT SIX-STORY HOTEL
BECAME FIVE STORIES.
- THAT SOUNDS PRETTY HORRIBLE.
- DON'T IT?
BLASTING THINGS TO BITS
IS LIKE A GAME TO HIM.
I BET ALL THE COMPLIMENTS
WE HEAPED ON HIM
DURING THE GULF WAR HELPED
TO FUEL THAT FIRE.
SUDDENLY,
ALL HE WANTED WAS TO SEE
COOLER AND COOLER EXPLOSIONS.
AND KOKO JUST ENCOURAGED HIM.
SHE WAS A SULLEN LITTLE BRAT
AT THE TIME,
BUT WILEE'S "ART" PUT HER
IN A BETTER MOOD.
FROM THERE, IT JUST KEPT GOING.
THE NEXT INCIDENT TOOK PLACE
IN A NORTH AFRICAN--
- THERE'S MORE?
- Koko: ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
TAKE A LOAD OFF.
- DAMN, I AM STARVING.
- STRETCH MY LEGS.
IT'S GOOD TO GET OUT
OF THERE FOR A MINUTE.
- PARDON, MS. HEKMATYAR,
WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
FOR ME TO CALL MY WIFE?
- OH, BY ALL MEANS.
GO RIGHT AHEAD.
- JONAH, WANT AN ICE COLD
GRAPE SODA?
- OKAY, THANKS.
- ARE YOU SCARED OF ME?
AW, LEHM, I DON'T SUPPOSE
YOU'VE BEEN FILLING
THE KID'S HEAD
WITH STORIES ABOUT ME?
- SORRY, SOLDIER,
THAT'S CLASSIFIED.
- ( all laughing )
- OH, THAT LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE.
THIS IS TRUCK ONE TO KOKO.
I'D LIKE US TO SLOW TO A STOP
IN ABOUT 60 SECONDS.
- NO PROBLEM, WILEE.
YOU SENSING A TRAP?
- YEP, CAN'T SAY
ANYTHING FOR SURE,
BUT THE TURN IN THE ROAD UP
AHEAD JUST SCREAMS AMBUSH TO ME.
I'LL DO A SWEEP TO SEE
IF THEY'VE PLANTED ANY BOMBS
- ( groaning )
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- WELL, IF THAT'S WHAT
YOUR GUT'S TELLING YOU,
EXCALIBUR IS BACK.
THEY'VE CONTACTED THE GROUP
THAT WENT AHEAD OF US
AND ARE PLANNING
A PINCER ATTACK.
THAT IS NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
WE'LL HIT THEM FIRST.
ALL TRUCKS HALT!
LEHM, LUTZ, RIFLES.
- ( groaning )
HERE WE GO.
- NAZAL, ALL PHONE COMMUNICATION
IS NOW OFF-LIMITS, GOT IT?
- UNDERSTOOD.
VERY IMPRESSIVE, HCLI.
YOU IDENTIFIED THE AMBUSH POINT
BEFORE YOU EVEN GOT CLOSE.
WAS IT INSTINCT?  EXPERIENCE?
EXCALIBUR DOESN'T
STAND A CHANCE.
- MOVE, MOVE!
- Man: WHY ARE THEY ALL GETTING
OUT OF THEIR LORRIES?
- CONTACT NAZAL.
- I TRIED.
SON OF A BITCH AIN'T
PICKING UP.
- THEN CALL THE BLOODY TEAM
COMING FROM BEHIND.
- DAMN, IT'S HOT.
- WHAT'S THIS ONE UP TO?
- YOU WANT I SHOULD SNIPE HIM?
- YOU TWAT.
THAT WOULD DEFEAT THE WHOLE
PURPOSE OF STAGING THIS AMBUSH.
- THIS FEELS RIGHT.
LEAST IT'S WHERE
I'D HAVE PLANTED 'EM.
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
FROM THE LOOKS OF IT, I'D SAY
THERE'S MORE ACROSS THE ROAD.
- Man: WHAT THE FUCK?
IS HE MESSING AROUND
WITH OUR IED?
- WHOA!  DON'T UNDERESTIMATE
THE PINCER ATTACK.
THEY ARE SO DEAD.
OI, WE SHOULD KIDNAP
THAT ARMS DEALER.
BET SHE'LL FETCH
A PRETTY RANSOM.
- YEAH, WE'LL ALL GET RICH OFF
THAT STUCK-UP BINT.
- WE GOT A PROBLEM
NEITHER THE AMBUSH TEAM
NOR NAZAL'S RESPONDING
AND THE CONVOY'S
STOPPED UP AHEAD.
- WORTHLESS FUCKING TWITS.
WE'LL JUST KILL THEM, TOO.
HUH?  WAIT, IS THAT THEM
RIGHT THERE--
- OH!
- WE'VE GOT INCOMING FIRE.
- Koko: LOOK OUT FOR THAT
M2 AUTO-CANNON.
DON'T LET 'EM USE IT.
- ON IT.
- SHIT'S HITTING THE FAN NOW.
- OI, WHERE'D THAT ONE
GET OFF TO?
- COVER FIRE.  WASTE HIM
AS SOON AS YOU SEE HIM.
- COME ON, DON'T TELL ME YOU
JOKERS ARE ALL JUST TALK.
- AH.  FOUND HIM.  RIGHT THERE.
- BLOW HIS ASS TO KINGDOM COME.
SO LONG, PRICK.
- ( laughs )
- WE LOST ALL CONTACT
WITH THE AMBUSH TEAM.
- IT'S ALL GONE TITS UP.
- IS HE STILL ALIVE?
SEND HIM OUT.
- THE GUYS BEHIND US HAVE
STOPPED SHOOTING
WILEE, THEY HAVE A HUMAN BOMB.
- ROGER, I'M ON MY WAY.  JUST
WHEN I THOUGHT THESE LOWLIFES
COULDN'T GET ANY SCUMMIER.
- Koko: HE DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
EXCALIBUR.  MUST BE A LOCAL.
WE ALMOST SHOT
THE POOR MAN DOWN.
- HAVE YOU GUYS FULLY SECURED
THIS SIDE OF THE ROAD?
- SURE HAVE.
- THAT'S GOOD.
( sighs ) DAMN THIS HEAT.
MAO, UGO, I NEED YOU TO RUN OVER
TO THAT MOUNTAIN
AND BRING BACK SOMEONE
WHO STILL HAS A PULSE.
- Both: ROGER THAT.
- ALLAH.
WHY IS IT YOU PUT ME
THROUGH THIS TRIAL?
- FALL DOWN.  TRIP AND ROLL
IN THIS DIRECTION.
- WHAT?  ARE YOU CRAZY?
THIS BOMB WILL EXPLODE
IF I DO THAT.
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
JUST DROP AND ROLL NOW.
- Ugo:
MAN, IT'S A TOTAL BLOODBATH.
- Mao:
THINK THERE ARE ANY SURVIVORS?
NOT TO BE RUDE, NAZAL,
BUT WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- THAT MAN RIGHT THERE
IS STILL BREATHING.
HE'S EXCALIBUR'S PRESIDENT.
I BELIEVE HE COULD BE EFFECTIVE.
NOW WOULD YOU BE SO KIND AS TO
LET ME HAVE THE MAN TO HIS LEFT?
HIS FATHER WORKS
IN ENGLAND'S HOME OFFICE
AND THE FAMILY IS RICH.
- DUMB BASTARD.
FELL ON HIS ASS.
- FUCK ME!  THIS SUCKS.
WHAT HAPPENED?
THESE BLOKES WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE EASY MARKS,
BUT THEY PRETTY MUCH WIPED US
OUT IN MINUTES.
NOW WE'RE STUCK IN THE DESERT
WITH NOWHERE TO RUN.
- WELL, DON'T BITCH
TO ME ABOUT IT.
- MAKE THE CALL.
DETONATE THE BOMB.
- ( rings )
- ( laughs )
LEAVE A MESSAGE.
- IT AIN'T GOING OFF.
FUCK!
- ( footsteps approaching )
- SOMEONE'S COMING.
- AW, BOLLOCKS.
WAIT, THAT'S THE BOSS MAN?
- NEED A HAND HERE, MATES.
COULD YOU GET THIS VEST OFF ME?
- Wilee: DAMN IT.
THAT TOTALLY FREAKED JONAH OUT.
WHY DO I ALWAYS LOSE CONTROL
WHEN IT COMES TO PYRO?
WHAT IF HE DOESN'T TAKE
MY LANGUAGE LESSONS
SERIOUSLY ANYMORE?
- I'VE REALLY GOTTA START TAKING
WILEE'S TUTORING MORE SERIOUSLY.
GUY IS DANGEROUS.
- ( theme music playing )
- Nazal:
THE PAST TWO WEEKS
SPENT INFILTRATING
EXCALIBUR PAID OFF.
YOU HAVE MY GRATITUDE,
MS. HEKMATYAR.
NOW WOULD YOU MIND TERRIBLY
IF I ABANDONED MY POST
AS TRUCK DRIVER?
- OF COURSE, YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
WE'LL BE JUST FINE WITHOUT YOU.
THEIR HUMAN BOMB WAS SOME RANDOM
TRUCK DRIVER THEY KIDNAPPED.
- I'M GLAD TO HEAR THAT.
YOUR DESTINATION IS NOT MUCH
FARTHER, BUT USE CAUTION.
SO LONG.
- THE PEOPLE OF THIS COUNTRY
DO POSSESS QUITE
THE ENTREPRENEURIAL SPIRIT.
- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS
LOCO, I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS LOCO,
I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪