- THE C.I.A. HAS FOUR DISTINCT
TYPES OF POSITION
THAT OVERSEE THEIR SPIES.
BUT THE KIND THAT MAKE ME
WANNA TURN AND RUN
WHEN I ENCOUNTER THEM
IN THE FIELD
IS THE P.O.O.--
THE PARAMILITARY.
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO CARRY OUT
THE AGENCY'S COMBAT OPERATIONS.
- Man: HEX?
WHAT, LIKE A HEXAGON?
- NAH, IT'S GERMAN.
SHORT FOR, LIKE, WITCH.
- ( gun fires )
- JUST PUTTING A BULLET IN KOKO
WON'T BE ANY FUN.
I HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT IN THIS WORLD
WOULD HURT HER MOST...
AND THEN DESTROY IT.
- ♪... TIME TIME TIME TIME
TO ATTACK. ♪
- I THINK WE TOOK
A WRONG TURN BACK THERE.
- Lutz: WHAT?
- ( tires screech )
- ALL THE DAMN ROADS
LOOK THE SAME.
I COULDN'T HELP IT.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT,
LITTLE LADY.
NO ONE'S ON YOUR CASE
ABOUT THIS.
- Jonah: IT'S PRETTY HERE.
- MAKES YOU WONDER WHY
PEOPLE WOULD CHOOSE
A PLACE LIKE THIS
TO FIGHT A WAR.
YOU KNOW, A FEW A YEARS
BEFORE YOU WERE BORN,
THIS VALLEY WAS THE SITE
OF EUROPE'S BLOODIEST BATTLE
SINCE WORLD WAR II.
- WELL,
IT MAKES PERFECT SENSE TO ME.
EVERYONE FIGHTS OVER IT
BECAUSE THEY WANT THE BEAUTY
ALL TO THEMSELVES.
- GOOD POINT.
GUESS I NEVER
LOOKED AT IT THAT WAY.
YOU'RE A WISE KID.
- ( theme music playing )
- SOCCHI REPORTING,
AS REQUESTED, SIR.
- HE'S YOUNG.
STILL FOLLOWS ORDERS.
SEEMS WE'RE OFF
TO A GOOD START.
- THIS IS
SERGEANT RENATO SOCCHI.
HE RUNS OUR INTEL GATHERING OPS
ON THE LOCALS.
- HELLO,
MY NAME IS GEORGE BLACK.
I HEAR YOU'RE GOOD
WITH GROUND INTEL.
YOU MIND GIVING ME A HAND
FOR A BIT?
- Man: BLACK IS C.I.A.,
SERGEANT. HELP HIM.
THE ITALIAN ARMY'S ALWAYS HAPPY
TO RELAY VITAL INTELLIGENCE
TO OUR AMERICAN FRIENDS.
PLEASE GIVE MR. BLACK
EVERYTHING HE NEEDS.
- UH, RIGHT.
I'LL DO MY BEST, SIR.
- ( car starts )
- OWE YA ONE.
- GRAZIE, BURATTINAIO.
- "PUPPETMASTER," HUH?
- IT'S A NICKNAME,
RENATO.
YOU'RE MORE THAN WELCOME
TO COME UP WITH YOUR OWN FOR ME.
WE'LL BE WORKING TOGETHER
FOR A WHILE.
- THE NAME I CAME UP
WITH FOR HIM WAS "SAW".
AT THAT POINT, A JAGGED
BLADE WAS HOW I VIEWED
THE C.I.A.'S TACTICS.
BUT SAW WAS CAREFUL,
PRECISE.
WITH MY INTEL,
HE ORCHESTRATED THE KILLINGS
OF DOZENS
OF BOSNIAN WAR CRIMINALS.
I QUICKLY UNDERSTOOD
WHY OTHERS CALLED HIM
"THE PUPPETEER."
HE CONTROLLED AN ARMY
OF AGENTS IN THE REGION.
AND THE FUEL
THAT KEPT THEM MOVING,
AND HIM POWERFUL,
WAS INFORMATION.
I NEVER QUITE KNEW HOW MANY
OTHER AGENTS HE HAD LIKE ME.
BUT I DO KNOW HE CONTROLLED
ALL OF US,
MANIPULATING OUR HEARTS
AND MINDS PERFECTLY,
ALL FOR THE GREATER MISSION.
AND WITH HIS MANY SUCCESSES,
SAW QUICKLY ROSE
THROUGH THE RANKS.
- ( tires squeal )
- AHH, SON OF A--
( thinking ) WHERE IS
THE PEACEKEEPING FORCE?
DAMN IT!
"KILL ANYONE SUSPICIOUS."
THOSE WERE ALWAYS
THE BAD GUYS' ORDERS.
I WATCHED HELPLESSLY
AS THE MILITIA
IN THE REPUBLIC OF T
EXECUTED EVERY CIVILIAN
WHO EVEN LOOKED AT THEM FUNNY.
THAT MEANT IT WAS ONLY
A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THE NUMBER CAME UP
ON MY SOURCE AND HIS FAMILY.
- ( tires squeal )
- ( blades whirring )
- TOO SLOW!
SPEED IS WHAT KEEPS
YOUR SOURCES ALIVE.
IF YOU'RE EVEN A HALF SECOND
SLOWER THAN YOUR ENEMIES,
YOU'LL BE ZIPPING YOUR CIVILIAN
FRIENDS INTO BODY BAGS!
I THINK IT'S TIME
YOU LOST THAT UNIFORM
AND OFFICIALLY
JOINED THE COMPANY.
IT'LL BE FUN.
- R: ALL MY RECORDS FROM WHEN I
WAS IN THE BERSAGLIERI ARE REAL.
BUT EVERYTHING AFTER, UP THROUGH
JOINING KOKO'S CREW, IS FAKE.
I WORK FOR SAW.
I CAN'T BETRAY HIM.
- Black: THIRD SPECIAL OPS,
WIDE-RANGE
RADIO COMM PLATOON.
THE SO-CALLED W.W. PLATOON
WAS AN ABORTED ATTEMPT
TO CREATE
AN ALL-FEMALE SPECIAL OPS GROUP
MADE UP ENTIRELY
OF WEST POINT GRADS.
HEX HAD ALREADY MADE LIEUTENANT
WHEN SHE GOT THE CALL.
THE SQUAD DID SO WELL,
THEY WERE EVEN ALLOWED
TO WEAR GREEN BERET KIT.
BUT THE UNIT
NEVER HAD FULL BACKING.
BRASS SHUT IT DOWN WHEN TOO
MANY OF THE WOMEN DROPPED OUT.
AT LEAST,
THAT WAS THEIR OFFICIAL REASON.
THE TRUTH IS, MANY GENERALS
SIMPLY REMAINED UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH FEMALE SOLDIERS,
SO THEY COOKED UP AN EXCUSE.
TO KEEP THE WOMEN QUIET,
THEY WERE BOUGHT OFF
WITH PROMOTIONS.
EXCEPT FOR HEX.
SHE REBELLED AND QUIT.
THAT'S WHEN A RECRUITER
FOR THE COMPANY
INVITED HER INTO THE SPY GAME.
I MET WITH HER MYSELF
AROUND THAT TIME
TO FEEL HER OUT.
SHE STRUCK ME AS A TRUE PATRIOT.
CONFIDENT TOO.
HEX CAME RIGHT OUT
AND SAID
SHE WAS A BETTER SOLDIER
THAN ANY MAN.
THE MORNING OF 9/11,
HEX'S FIANCE DIED
IN ONE OF THE TOWERS.
SHE WAS ALREADY IN EASTERN
EUROPE, SERVING AS A P.O.O.,
SO SHE FLEW TO AFGHANISTAN
AND PROMPTLY WENT TO WORK.
BUT EVEN IN THOSE CRAZY DAYS,
HER BRAND OF TERRORIST HUNTING
STARTED SKIRTING
INTERNATIONAL LAW.
SHE DEEPLY LOVES THIS COUNTRY,
BUT THE FEELING'S NOT MUTUAL.
SHE'S BECOME SO DESTRUCTIVE,
I'VE BEEN ORDERED
TO KEEP HER UNDER MY THUMB.
SO I INCLUDED HEX
IN OPERATION UNDERSHAFT.
THIS WAY, I CAN KEEP HER FROM
USING COUNTER-TERRORISM
AS AN EXCUSE TO DESTROY
A PERFECTLY GOOD ARMS NETWORK.
- ( cell phone vibrating )
- YEAH, THIS IS HEX.
GOODNESS.
I CERTAINLY HAVEN'T HEARD
FROM YOU IN A LONG TIME.
- YOU'RE DOING WELL, I HOPE?
I'M AFRAID
SOMETHING URGENT'S COME UP.
I WAS WONDERING, HAVE YOU
SENT OUT ANY HIT MEN LATELY?
AFTER THE ARMS DEALER
KOKO HEKMATYAR?
- I DON'T FOLLOW, CHIEF.
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU TRYING
TO GET AT HERE?
OH, WAIT.  I SEE.
OPERATION UNDERSHAFT IS REALLY
ALL ABOUT HEKMATYAR, ISN'T IT?
BACK IN EASTERN EUROPE,
WE MAY HAVE HAD OUR DIFFERENCES,
BUT I ASSURE YOU,
ORDERING A HIT
HASN'T EVEN CROSSED MY MIND
THIS TIME AROUND.
- THEN EVERYTHING IS CALM.
THAT'S GOOD.
LET'S KEEP IT THAT WAY.
BYE, HEX.
- ( laughing )
SPY MASTER.
ONE LITTLE PHONE CALL,
AND CHIEF BLACK
COMPLETELY TIES MY HANDS.
AT LEAST HE HOPES SO.
BUT I'VE GOT A LOOPHOLE.
THERE ARE WAYS TO
DESTROY PEOPLE'S LIVES
WITHOUT KILLING THEM.
- ( gunfire )
- YOU'D THINK AN ARMS DEALER
WOULD BE MORE CAUTIOUS
ABOUT USING UP HER OWN PRODUCT.
WE'VE GOT A SNIPER!
SMOKE GRENADE.
COVER US!
- OH!
- DAMN IT.
I SAID "SNIPER."
EVERYONE ON THE CHANNEL,
LAUREN'S DEAD.
- ( gunfire continues )
- ( gun firing )
- ( grunts )
- ( bullet zings )
- ( thinking ) MOTHERFUCKER!
EVEN WITH THE SMOKE COVER,
THEY'RE TRACKING OUR OUTLINES
IN THE MOONLIGHT.
SHE MUST HAVE GUYS
WITH SPECIAL OPS EXPERIENCE.
IF WE CAN'T
TURN THE TABLES AGAIN,
WE'LL GO FROM HUNTERS,
TO HUNTED, TO DEAD.
KOKO HEKMATYAR,
THE ARMS DEALER, THE TERRORIST.
I CAN'T LET YOU LIVE.
( aloud ) DON'T STOP SHOOTING
UNTIL THEY'RE ALL DEAD!
- Men: HA!
- MOVE.
- Echo:
YOU'RE AMERICAN TOO, HUH?
EITHER WAY, I CAN'T LET YOU
KILL THE LITTLE LADY.
- ( fires )
- ( gasps )
- ( thinking )
I JUST CAN'T SEEM TO SLEEP
WHEN THERE'S A FULL MOON.
- ( panting )
I'M SCARED.
PLEASE SAVE ME, VALMET!
I DON'T WANT TO DIE!
I'M PAYING YOU.
YOU HAVE TO SAVE ME!
- Valmet: KOKO!
- Echo: DON'T CRY, LITTLE LADY.
- ( gun rattles )
I GOT YOUR BACK.
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO PAY ME
ONE RED CENT TO DO IT, EITHER.
- ECHO, HAVE YOU BEEN SHOT?
OH GOD.  ECHO!
- BUT I DO
HAVE JUST ONE CONDITION.
WHAT DO I ALWAYS TELL YOU?
A LEADER SHOULD ALWAYS SMILE,
NOT SCOWL AND THREATEN.
THAT IS THE KEY
TO THE LIFE WE LEAD.
- Koko: I JUST CAN'T SEEM TO
SLEEP WHEN THERE'S A FULL MOON.
- Amalia: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I LOVE YOU, KOKO.
- MY PLEASURE.
I'M GLAD YOU DECIDED
TO GO WITH US, MS. TOROHOVSKY.
- YOU'RE A REAL LIFE-SAVER.
WITH THE NEW REGULATIONS,
I COULD NEVER
HAVE IMPORTED THESE.
AND I DO LOVE
JAPANESE CRAFTSMANSHIP.
BY THE WAY, YOU HAVEN'T
DONE ANYTHING UNTOWARD LATELY,
- HAVE YOU?
- Huh? ( laughs )
- NO,
I'VE BEEN EXCEEDINGLY BORING.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
- A FRIEND OF MINE
IN FRANCE'S GENERAL DIRECTORATE
FOR EXTERNAL SECURITY,
WELL, HE SAYS THAT YOU
HAVE SOME C.I.A. TRACKING YOU
AND THAT ALL OF THEM
ARE TOP-NOTCH AGENTS.
SOME OF THE SCARIEST HARD-ASSES
HE'S EVER SEEN.
PLEASE, BE CAREFUL, KOKO.
- ( thinking ) IF SHE HEARD THAT
FROM THE D.G.S.E.,
THEY'RE SNOOPING AROUND
MY BUSINESS TOO.
I THINK IT'S TIME
WE GOT OUT OF FRANCE.
- C.I.A. ARE THE HARDEST PESTS
FOR A BUSINESSWOMAN
TO SHAKE, YES?
THERE WAS ONE
WHO LATCHED ON TO ME.
WHAT DID HE GO BY?
BOOK MAN, I THINK?
- Koko: YES, BOOK MAN.
REAL NAME, GEORGE BLACK.
RUNS THE EUROPEAN BRANCH
OF THE NATIONAL
CLANDESTINE SERVICE.
ISN'T HE THE GUY WHO MADE A NAME
FOR HIMSELF
RUNNING INTEL
DURING THE YUGOSLAV WARS?
- YES. YOU CERTAINLY KNOW
YOUR ENEMIES. THAT'S MY KOKO.
I ONCE GOT MIXED UP
WITH GEORGE
WHEN HE WAS WORKING
OUT OF HIS AGENCY'S ROME BRANCH.
HE'S AN OLD SCHOOL,
COLD WARRIOR-TYPE.
THINKS HE CAN PULL THE STRINGS
ON ARMS DEALERS
LIKE THEY'RE PUPPETS.
LUCKY FOR ME,
MY D.G.S.E. FRIENDS
GOT HIM OFF MY BACK.
A GUY LIKE HIM
PULLING OUR STRINGS?
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( both laughing )
- Lehm: YOU TWO SEEM
TO BE GETTING ALONG.
- I JUST THINK
SHE'S AN INTERESTING PERSON.
I DON'T KNOW. SHE THE KIND OF
WOMAN WHO COULD DO ANYTHING--
ARMS DEALING JUST HAPPENS TO BE
WHERE SHE WOUND UP.
- FUNNY YOU SAY THAT, KOKO.
I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT
THE SAME ABOUT YOU.
- NAH.
THIS IS THE ONLY PATH FOR ME.
- YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- ( gun firing )
- Tojo: CRAZY TO THINK
WE'RE IN AN AGE
WHERE EVEN MAGAZINES
ARE PLASTIC.
- GREAT, ISN'T IT?
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'M SETTING ALL OF YOU GUYS UP
WITH BRAND NEW GEAR.
SAY HELLO TO YOUR NEW LITTLE
FRIEND, THE MAGPUL MASADA.
- All: OOOH!
- GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
I WAS KIND OF WORRIED
YOU WERE ALL GONNA GO, "'KAY."
- IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'VE BEEN HAVING
ANY PROBLEMS WITH
THE CURRENT RIFLES.
- AHA!
I KNEW YOU WOULD SAY SOMETHING
LIKE THAT, JONAH.
MY PLAN IS FOR THE WHOLE
UNIT TO USE THE SAME TYPE
OF AMMO AND MAGAZINES.
THAT WAY WE CAN ALWAYS
HELP EACH OTHER OUT IN A PINCH.
- MMM.
- Lutz: THIS GONNA GO
FOR SIDEARMS TOO, LITTLE LADY?
- FUNNY YOU SHOULD ASK.
THIS IS YOUR NEW HANDGUN.
THE SIG SAUER S.P. 2022.
LIKE WITH THE RIFLES,
THE IDEA IS FOR EVERYONE
TO USE THE SAME CALIBER ROUNDS.
ANYONE WHO WASN'T
USING .9mm BEFORE, YOU ARE NOW.
- WELL, DON'T JUST SHOW IT OFF,
FIRE SOME ROUNDS.
- ( laughs )
ALL RIGHTY.
IF YOU CAN'T MATCH MY SHOOTING,
YOU'LL BE PUNISHED.
- AW, THANKS
FOR OPENING YOUR BIG MOUTH, R.
NOW WE GOTTA PLAY HER GAME.
- Ugo: THAT MIGHT BE IMPOSSIBLE.
- ( tires squeal )
- TOO SLOW, BOYS!
AT THIS RATE,
YOU'LL BE SHOT TO PIECES.
- JONAH, WRONG SPOT.
- OH, SORRY.
- RUN THE DRILL AGAIN.
- ( tires squeal )
- OH, SHIT. SORRY!
- AW, COME ON.
- Lehm: DON'T LET THE PERSON
YOU'RE PROTECTING FALL.
- LUTZ, SON OF A BITCH!
- DUDE,
THAT'S WHY I SAID I'M SORRY.
OH, MAN, YOU LOOK
LIKE FREAKIN' TWO-FACE.
- Tojo: DON'T LAUGH.
IT'S YOUR FAULT.
- OH, COME ON NOW, GUYS.
DON'T WANT
ANY TWO-FACES HERE.
- Lehm: ALL RIGHT, AGAIN.
LIVE AMMO THIS TIME.
- LET ME GET SOME WATER FIRST,
CHIEF.
- R?
- WHAT'S UP?
- YOU KNOW A C.I.A. AGENT?
PEOPLE CALL HIM BOOK MAN?
- YEAH, I'M FAMILIAR WITH HIM.
MET HIM IN BOSNIA,
WHEN I WAS STILL ITALIAN ARMY.
HE NEEDED SOME INTELLIGENCE
I HAD ON LOCAL WARLORDS,
SO I HELPED HIM OUT
A FEW TIMES.
BOOK MAN, BURATTINAIO,
ADEEB.
HIS REAL NAME WAS--
- MISTER GEORGE BLACK.
NOW HE RUNS HIS OWN BRANCH.
- WELL THEN,
YOU'VE ALREADY
DONE YOUR HOMEWORK.
- I'VE HEARD RUMORS
ABOUT HIM TRACKING US,
SO I WANTED TO SEE
WHAT YOU KNEW
SINCE I FIGURED YOU'D
ACTUALLY MET HIM IN PERSON.
- WELL, I CAN TELL YOU
HE'S A BIG EATER.
HE HAD A LITTLE GUT
ON HIM THEN,
SO BY NOW
HE COULD LOOK LIKE SANTA CLAUS.
- I GUESS WORKING FOR THE C.I.A.
MAKES YOU STRESS-EAT.
LOOK AT SCHOKOLADE.
- I KNOW BOOK MAN'S
GOOD WITH LANGUAGES.
HE MAJORED IN ARABIAN LITERATURE
AS AN UNDERGRAD,
SO THAT'S WHERE
THE ADEEB NICKNAME COMES FROM.
THAT'S WHAT HE TOLD ME,
THOUGH I THINK IT
MEANS SOMETHING ELSE.
SEE,
WHEN HE INVESTIGATES SOMETHING,
HE MAKES IT A POINT
TO LEARN EVERY DETAIL HE CAN,
LIKE A SCHOLAR.
- AH, GOOD TO KNOW.
- DOES THIS HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH WHAT THOSE HIT MEN SAID?
DIDN'T THEY MENTION SOMETHING
ABOUT THE C.I.A.?
- NO.  BOOK MAN
CAME UP IN SOME OTHER RUMORS.
I THINK THE HIT MAN STUFF
IS A COINCIDENCE.
I CAN'T SEE
SOMEONE AS HIGH UP
AS THE EURO BRANCH CHIEF
PLAYING THAT CARD.
EVER HEAR OF ANOTHER AGENT
WHO GOES BY HEX?
A PARAMILITARY
OPERATIONS OFFICER?
YOU KNOW, P.O.O.?
- SORRY, DON'T KNOW HIM.
DOES HIS FACE
HAVE SIX SIDES OR SOMETHING?
- SHE'S A SHE.
HEX AS IN WITCH.
- WHOA, FROM THE SOUND OF IT,
YOU'VE HAD A RUN-IN
WITH HER BEFORE.
WHY DON'T WE TALK
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE?
YOU KNOW,
SPARE YOU THE BAD MEMORIES.
AND DON'T FORGET,
YOU GOT US NOW.
NO MATTER HOW NASTY YOUR
ENEMIES MAY BE, LITTLE LADY,
THIS SQUAD WILL KEEP YOU SAFE.
- Lehm: R!
- YEAH?
- BURNIN' DAYLIGHT.
- COMING.
- TOO SLOW LIKE THAT,
JONAH.
TRACE OVER YOUR TARGET
WITH THE MUZZLE.
NICE AND SMOOTH.
SQUEEZE THE TRIGGER
JUST AS THEY MEET,
AND YOU'LL HIT CLEAN
EVERY TIME.  WATCH ME.
YOUR TARGETS'LL
ALMOST ALWAYS BE MOVING TOO.
IF YOU CAN'T KEEP UP,
YOU WON'T HIT 'EM.
- GOT IT.
- Both: DAMN, HE'S GOOD.
- ( thinking ) HEX.
WHO THE HELL IS SHE?
I HAVE TO KNOW.
- NO MATTER HOW MANY WE KILL,
THERE ARE ALWAYS MORE.
LIKE ROACHES.
WE CAN'T MAKE
ANY LASTING PROGRESS
AGAINST THEM
UNTIL WE FIND THE SOURCE.
YOU HEAR ME,
TEAM CUTTHROAT?
EVEN WHILE SERVING THE WORST
YEARS OF IRAQ AND AFGHANISTAN,
THE MILITARY COULDN'T ACCEPT
YOUR UNCONVENTIONAL METHODS.
ALWAYS HOUNDED BY THE M.P.s.
BUT NOW YOU'RE MY ARMY
AND YOUR METHODS ARE MY METHODS.
TEN-HUT!  MOVE OUT.
- ( all firing guns )
- Woman: WE HAVE VISUAL ON HEX
AND TEAM CUTTHROAT.
- ( cell phone vibrating )
- KEEP TRACKING THEM.
- HOW 'BOUT THIS ONE,
THIS ONE AND THAT?
- NO PROBLEM, MR. BLACK.
I'LL HAVE THAT RIGHT OUT.
- ( cell phone vibrating )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( European siren wailing )
- Black: HELLO, R.
- IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU PICKED UP THE PHONE.
WHEN WERE YOU PLANNING
ON ANSWERING MY QUESTION?
THINK I SENT YOU THAT FIRST TEXT
ABOUT 10 HOURS AGO.
YOU TAUGHT ME SPEED WAS
EVERYTHING IN THIS GAME.
SO MUCH FOR THAT.
- I THOUGHT YOU'D UNDERSTAND
THE DELAY IN MY RESPONSE
MEANT YOU WERE ASKING A QUESTION
I'M NOT ABLE TO ANSWER.
JUST KNOW
SHE'S A DEEP-COVER AGENT.
THAT'S ALL I CAN TELL YOU.
YOU KNOW HOW THIS WORKS.
I WOULDN'T TELL SOMEONE
ABOUT YOU, EITHER.
- YEAH, DEEP COVER, MY ASS.
SHE'S ACTING RIGHT OUT
IN THE OPEN.
WE'VE ALREADY HAD RUN-INS
WITH HER ASSASSINS.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHO I THINK SHE IS, SAW.
I THINK HEX IS THE ONE BEHIND
ALL THE RECENT ATTEMPTS
ON OUR GROUP.
ARE YOU OKAY WITH
SOME ROGUE AGENT
SCREWING OPERATION UNDERSHAFT?
BECAUSE YOU PROMISED
YOU WERE GONNA
GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
- I HEAR YOU, R.
I'LL CALL YOU BACK SOON.
R., YOU ARE MY RIGHT ARM
AND HEX IS MY LEFT.
AS SUCH, SHE WILL CONTINUE
TO BE A CRITICAL PLAYER
IN ALL
OF MY DEPARTMENT'S ACTIVITIES.
SHE'S STAYING
FOR THE LONG HAUL.
ESPECIALLY SINCE THAT LEFT ARM
IS ATTACHED TO A FIST
THAT SMASHES TERRORISTS.
IF SHE WANTS A SACRIFICE,
WE MAY HAVE TO GIVE IT TO HER.
EVEN IF IT'S THE LIFE
OF A SINGLE CHILD.
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS-- OH NO ♪
♪ NO NO
NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪