- KOKO, THIS WHOLE TIME
I'VE BEEN WORKING FOR BOOK MAN.
I'M A SPY.
I AM SO SORRY,
LITTLE LADY.
- R!
- Koko: DON'T LOSE HER.
IF YOU DO, I'LL COME DOWN THERE
AND BLOW YOUR BRAINS OUT MYSELF.
- I REALLY PISSED YOU OFF,
DIDN'T I, KOKO HEKMATYAR?
VERY WELL.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO OUR NEXT BATTLE IN HELL.
- R.
- ( theme music playing )
- Jonah: MY PARENTS WERE KILLED
BY A FIGHTER JET
JUST LIKE THAT ONE,
FULLY EQUIPPED
WITH THE LATEST TECHNOLOGY
AND A PAYLOAD
OF LASER-GUIDED SMART BOMBS.
THE PEOPLE WHO INVENT WEAPONS,
WHO CONSTRUCT THEM,
WHO SELL THEM,
WHO USE THEM--
I HATE THEM.
I WILL ALWAYS HATE THEM.
SO MAYBE
THIS IS GOD
PLAYING A TWISTED JOKE ON ME.
- Koko: STEP LIVELY,
OFFICER JONAH.
LET'S GO--
ONE, TWO, ONE, TWO.
RIGHT, LEFT,
RIGHT, LEFT.
- THIS IS KOKO HEKMATYAR,
A SELLER OF WEAPONS.
HERE I AM,
TRAVELING WITH AN ARMS DEALER.
- MMM.
THE MEETING--
THEY'RE LATE.
- YES, THEY ARE.
- ( ringing )
- I HAVE A MESSAGE
FOR MR. KASPER HEKMATYAR.
- ( sighs )
THE WEATHER, LIKE OUR
NEGOTIATIONS, IS A WASH.
- HA!  YEAH, GOOD ONE, BOSS.
REAL CLEVER.
- YOU THINK SO?
- IT WAS ALL RIGHT.
- OH YEAH, CHEQUITA?
TOO BAD.
I THOUGHT THAT GRIN
WAS FOR ME.
WE'LL DROWN LIKE RATS
BEFORE WE REACH THE CAR.
LET'S HAVE LUNCH
AND WAIT OUT THE STORM.
- Bodyguards:
HELL YEAH, SOUNDS GOOD!
- Chequita:
I COULD GO FOR SOME FOOD.
- I'LL HAVE A CHICKEN
AND LETTUCE BURGER,
A TOMATO CHEESEBURGER
AND A SHAVED ICE
WITH EVERY FLAVOR ON IT.
- GOT IT.
- WOW, IS ALL THAT GONNA BE
JUST FOR YOU, BOSS?
BURGERS AND SHAVED ICE?
YOU'RE GONNA DIE YOUNG.
- MUCH AS I APPRECIATE
YOUR EXPERT OPINIONS,
I BELIEVE I CAN ORDER
FOR MYSELF.
- DOUBLE FRIED RICE,
CURRY OVER RICE, SATAY,
AND SHAVED ICE.
- OOH, LOOKS GREAT.
- THANK YOU FOR THIS FOOD.
- YEAH, AMEN.
- Guard: THIS IS AMAZING!
- OH, BY THE WAY,
ONE OF MY SISTER'S GUYS, R,
WAS SHOT DOWN IN AN AMBUSH.
STORY HAS IT
HE SINGLE-HANDEDLY WENT UP
AGAINST A BADASS P.O.O.
AND 10 OF HER MEN.
- TO R.
- All: TO R!
- HE WAS A GOOD SOLDIER.
- Guard: P.O.O?
YOU MEAN LIKE THE C.I.A.?
PARAMILITARY OPS OFFICERS
ARE SERIOUS BUSINESS.
- Guard #2: THAT'S AN ELITE
OUTFIT, DANGEROUS AS ALL HELL.
- Chequita:
MMM, DAMN, THIS IS GOOD.
- Waitress: TOMATO
CHEESEBURGER'S COMING OUT.
- Kasper:
PUT IT RIGHT HERE, DARLIN'.
- SO HOW DO YOU THINK
TOJO'S HOLDING UP?
AND MY LITTLE MISHKA?
- I'M SURE THE KID'S
DOING JUST FINE.
HE'S HARDCORE.
- YEAH, TOJO!
WE DIDN'T GET TO SEE HIM
LAST TIME WE WERE ONBOARD
THEIR SHIP, DID WE?
- WHO'S MISHKA?
- DUDE, YOU DON'T REMEMBER
THAT CHILD SOLDIER
WHO WIPED OUT OUR ENTIRE
DAMN BASE LAST SPRING?
COME ON.
- YEAH!
- Guard: DIDN'T WE DUMP HIM
IN A SHIPPING CONTAINER?
- Chequita: DAMN, IT'S REALLY
COMING DOWN OUT THERE.
SO BOSS, SPEAKING OF--
OUR SALES
ARE WAY DOWN TOO, HUH?
- ( coughs )
THAT WAS UNNECESSARILY BLUNT.
THANKS FOR THAT.
- All: SO DID
THE LAST-MINUTE CANCELLATION
OF THIS MORNING'S MEETING
HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH A CERTAIN JAPANESE FIRM?
- SEE?
WASN'T JUST ME THINKING THAT.
IT'S BEEN EATING AWAY
AT THESE POOR GUYS ALL DAY.
- YEAH.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU HAVE IT
PRETTY MUCH FIGURED OUT.
THE NUALKHAIR FAMILY--
ALL TOP MILITARY BRASS--
HAVE BEEN GOOD CUSTOMERS
OF MINE.
BUT APPARENTLY THIS FIRM
WANTS TO CHASE H.C.L.I.
OUT OF SOUTHEAST ASIA
ALTOGETHER.
SEEMS THEY'RE STARTING
TO VIEW US AS A THREAT.
IT'S A MESSAGE.
THEY'VE TRIED TO IGNORE US
AS LONG AS THEY COULD,
BUT WE'RE GETTING BIG
AND THEY DON'T LIKE IT.
SO WE CAN'T SEE THEM,
BUT THEY DO CAST A BIG SHADOW.
I HAD H.Q. LOOK INTO IT,
BUT THEY CAME UP EMPTY.
SAID, "THERE ARE NO FIRMS
LIKE THAT IN JAPAN."
SO DOES THAT MEAN
SOME KIND OF GHOST
IS INTERFERING
WITH MY BUSINESS?
OR IS IT
SOME LOST INITIATIVE
THAT EVEN THE JAPANESE
GOVERNMENT HAS FORGOTTEN
IT LAUNCHED
70 YEARS AGO,
AROUND WORLD WAR II.
THINK WHAT A PAIN IN THE ASS
THAT'D BE.
- SO NOW WHAT?
CAVE IN TO THEIR DEMANDS
AND PULL OUT OF SOUTHEAST ASIA?
- YEAH, RIGHT!
- ( all laugh )
- Chequita:
THANKS FOR THE GRUB.
- Guard: YEAH, DOES THIS JOINT
HAVE GREAT FOOD OR WHAT?
- HEY, LOOK,
THE SUN'S OUT.
- FOR NOW.
IT'S THE EYE OF THE STORM.
THIS IS A TYPHOON
AND IT'S FAR FROM OVER.
- THEN NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
SEEMS LIKE AN APPROPRIATE JOB
TO GET STARTED
UNDER THE COVER OF A STORM.
BY THE WAY, I'M BRINGING IN KOKO
TO ASSIST WITH THIS.
I'VE ALREADY MADE ARRANGEMENTS.
SHE AND HER TEAM SHOULD BE
LANDING IN JAPAN ANY TIME NOW.
- Chequita: WELL WELL,
YOU SEEM MIGHTY ENTHUSIASTIC.
- ( video game gunfire )
- SO ISN'T JAPAN WHERE
TOJO IS ORIGINALLY FROM?
- UH, YEAH, THAT SOUNDS RIGHT.
JAPAN, SUCH A SAFE PLACE.
IN FACT, THE ONLY THING THAT'S
TO DIE FOR THERE IS THE FOOD.
EXPENSIVE AS HELL, THOUGH.
- HUH.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU SEEM ALMOST HAPPY.
( laughs )
- Jonah: I GUESS.
- SO KOKO,
ONCE WE ARRIVE IN JAPAN,
ARE WE GONNA BE MEETING UP
WITH KASPER AND HIS CREW?
- YEAH, I GUESS SO.
- ARE YOU SURE
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
FOR JONAH TO SEE HIM AGAIN?
WHAT IF WE GET A REPEAT
OF THE LAST TIME THEY MET?
- KASPER!
- THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
JONAH'S ACTUALLY CONVINCED
HIMSELF HE WANTS TO SEE KASPER.
- ( thinking ) JAPAN.
THAT'S WHERE
THEY TOOK THOSE THREE KIDS.
MAURICE, ELINE, JANOT.
- DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD KIDS HERE, COMMANDER.
- THAT ONE'S A SOLDIER.
WE REQUESTED MORE MEN FROM H.Q.
AND THEY SENT OVER
SOME BRAT FROM THE ALPINE UNIT.
THE OTHER KIDS HERE
ARE ORPHANS, THOUGH.
- THE VICE COMMANDER'S COMING.
MALKA, HIDE THE FOOD!
- LET'S SEE IF YOU BRATS
ARE GOOD FOR ANYTHING
BUT EATIN' MY FOOD.
YOU AND YOU,
COME WITH ME.
GO.
- Both: SIR!
- ( girl crying )
- HOLD ON, I'LL COME TOO.
- SILENCE!
YOU'LL DO AS YOU'RE TOLD.
DO NOT QUESTION ME, EVER!
- SHOULDN'T WE BE GOING?
- DAMN KID CAN'T FOLLOW
A SIMPLE ORDER.
- JONATHAN!  JONATHAN!
- MALKA.  MALKA.
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE GONE WITH YOU.
I SHOULD HAVE FOUGHT HARDER.
I KNOW WHAT THEY DID.
I KNOW.
THEY MADE YOU WALK
THROUGH AN OLD MINEFIELD.
( crying )
MALKA, MALKA.
DAMN IT.
YOU DESERVED BETTER!
MAURICE,
LISTEN TO ME VERY CAREFULLY.
I NEED YOU TO TAKE ALL THE
CHILDREN TO OUR SECRET BASE.
DON'T LEAVE, NO MATTER WHAT.
- UH...
- ( gun cocking )
- HEY, YOU!
- ( gunfire )
- Jonah: NO MATTER WHAT.
- ( gunfire continues )
- WHERE'S THE SHOOTER?!
- Man: HOLD FIRE! YOU'RE
SHOOTING BLIND.
YOU'LL HIT EACH OTHER.
- ( gun cocks )
- Jonah: YOU'RE NO JOURNALIST.
WHO ARE YOU?
- I'M-- I'M AN ARMS DEALER.
EASY THERE.  YOU CAN SPARE
ONE LIFE, CAN'T YOU?
IF YOU DO, I KNOW,
YOU CAN HAVE THIS.  ALL OF IT.
- I DON'T WANT YOUR MONEY.
GIVE ME MALKA.
- UH, MALKA?
WHAT'S A MALKA?
- ( fires )
- MY NAME IS KASPER HEKMATYAR.
I'M AN ARMS DEALER.
WHO ARE YOU?
I DON'T SEE YOU
IN THESE RECORDS.
YOU AREN'T LISTED AMONG THE
SOLDIERS OR THE FOUR ORPHANS.
- IT'S NOT HARD, MISHKA,
HE'S JUST ASKING YOUR NAME.
GO ON.
- THREE.
THERE ARE
ONLY THREE ORPHANS NOW.
THAT BASTARD GASUD
KILLED MALKA.
- YOU HAVE TO ANSWER
FOR KILLING MY EMPLOYEE.
I'M CURIOUS,
HOW WILL YOU ACT
WHEN THE ENEMY YOU FACE IS FEAR?
- WAIT, HOLD ON,
ARE YOU GONNA KILL THEM?
THE OTHER CHILDREN?
KASPER!
AH!
- Kasper: YOU KNOW SOMETHING,
WE'LL NEVER SEE EYE TO EYE,
YOU AND ME.
I SEE WHY YOU'RE SO STRONG.
A BOY SOLDIER
FROM THE ALPINE UNIT.
I TOOK THE PRIVILEGE
OF LOOKING INTO YOU.
IT'S THE DAMNDEST THING.
TURNS OUT I WAS THE ONE
WHO SUPPLIED WEAPONS
TO THE MEN
WHO TARGETED YOUR VILLAGE.
SO, INDIRECTLY, AT LEAST,
I'M THE ONE
WHO KILLED YOUR PARENTS.
- YOU BASTARD!
( grunting )
- HAVE YOU GROWN TOO WEAK
TO TEAR AWAY MY FLESH
OR ARE YOU HOLDING BACK?
- ( sobbing )
- SEE,
THAT'S WHAT FEAR DOES TO YOU.
YOU SAT IN HERE FOR DAYS,
FEARING YOUR DEATH,
UNTIL YOU FINALLY FIGURED OUT
WHERE YOU REALLY STAND
IN THE WORLD.
YOU HAD TO DECIDE
WHICH WAS THE BETTER COURSE--
KILLING ME OR USING ME.
VERY WELL,
LET'S NEGOTIATE.
YOU SEE, I LIKE PEOPLE
WHO KNOW THEIR PLACE.
SO I'M CERTAIN WE CAN ARRIVE
AT TERMS
THAT ARE FAVORABLE
FOR US BOTH.
- THE OTHER KIDS,
WHERE ARE THEY?
- THEY'RE IN MY CUSTODY.
- SEND THEM SOMEPLACE SAFE,
SOMEWHERE THEY CAN BE HAPPY.
- MY TERRITORY RUNS
FROM HERE THROUGH MOST OF ASIA.
I'M SURE I CAN SET THEM
UP WITH GOOD HOMES
IN JAPAN OR SOMEWHERE.
CONSIDER IT DONE.
NOW WHAT DO YOU HAVE
TO OFFER ME?
- I HAVE NOTHING TO TRADE.
- NOT TRUE.  YOU HAVE
YOUR SKILL AS A SOLDIER.
YOU'D WORK WELL
AS A PERSONAL SECURITY GUARD.
SOUND GOOD?
GREAT,
THEN WE HAVE A DEAL.
THE SISTER I MENTIONED
HAS A PLACE FOR YOU.
NOW I ALREADY KNOW THE ANSWER,
BUT I WANT TO HEAR IT FROM YOU.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- MY NAME IS--
- Koko:
JONAH.  JONAH?
YOO-HOO.
- WHAT'S UP?
- LOOK, WE'RE IN JAPAN.
AND WE GOT SOME TIME TO KILL
BEFORE OUR NEXT JOB.
SO UNTIL THEN, WE'RE GONNA GO
OUT AND TRY AND HAVE SOME FUN.
- Chequita: JUST BEFORE GO TIME,
THIS AREA'S GONNA LOSE POWER.
OUR TARGET IS COLONEL
NUALKHAIR'S SON, KORWIT.
HE'S ON VACATION
AT THE FAMILY VILLA,
SO GIVE HIM
THE DELUXE TREATMENT.
- ( gulping )
HEY, WHERE THE FUCK
DID AGUS RUN OFF TO, BRO?
- HUH? DUDE, HE'S
UP IN HIS ROOM,
PROBABLY BALLS
DEEP IN TRIS.
TOO BAD THE WEATHER SUCKS ASS
WHILE WE'RE HERE.
WELL,
WE'LL JUST HAVE TO GET WASTED.
- FUCKIN' A, BRO!
- ( both laughing )
- HOT CHICK ON THE NEWS
SAYS THE STORM'LL BE OVER
BY TOMORROW.
- SWEET, I THINK
WE GOT ENOUGH BOOZE
TO LAST US
TILL THE SUN COMES OUT.
EH...
- WHAT THE FUCK?
- AW, LAME, DUDE,
THE POWER'S OUT.
- YOU GUYS GOT ANY
CANDLES AROUND HERE?
- BEATS ME, YO.
BUT LET ME KNOW
WHAT YOU FIND.
- OH, THIS REALLY BLOWS.
- ( firing with silencer )
- ARGH, CAN'T SEE JACK SHIT!
HOW DO YOU
NOT HAVE A FLASHLIGHT?
SERIOUSLY, THERE BETTER--
SOY SAUCE?
WHO KEEPS SOY SAUCE
IN A DRAWER?
- ( glass shattering )
- BRO? WHAT'D YOU
BREAK, DUMBASS?
COME ON,
MY PARENTS ARE GONNA BE PISSED.
HEY!
QUIT MESSIN' AROUND, DUDE.
- Chequita:
AH, THE GUEST OF HONOR.
- HUH?
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S FINISH UP HERE.
- Kasper: COPS'LL LOOK AT THIS
AS A MERE BURGLARY-GONE-WRONG.
ONLY THE GHOST WILL KNOW IT'S
REALLY A DECLARATION OF WAR.
- ( dialing )
- HEY, KOKO.
IT'S ME, KASPER.
THE OPERATION IS UNDERWAY.
SO HOW'S JAPAN?
IT'S RAINING CATS
AND DOGS HERE.
HEY, THANKS FOR WAITING.
SORRY TO MAKE YOU COME
ALL THE WAY OUT HERE TO MEET US.
I KNOW IT'S A PAIN.
- YEAH, SERIOUSLY.
- Woman over P.A.:
ATTENTION, PASSENGERS--
- SO, KOKO, YOU STARTED PLAYING
AS SOON AS YOU HIT
TOKYO, DIDN'T YOU?
- ( laughs ) YOU BET.
WE HIT BOTH THE LAND
AND SEA PARKS.
HEY, WAIT,
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
LAND AND SEA.  SOUNDS LIKE
THEY'RE THE MILITARY.
HEH!  WHAT'S NEXT?
AN AIR FORCE THEME PARK?
- EVER SINCE WE LOST R,
KOKO'S BEEN WORKING HARD
TO KEEP UP MORALE
BY TAKING US TO THEME PARKS.
AS IF THEY WEREN'T FUN ENOUGH
ON THEIR OWN,
KOKO'S HIGH SPIRITS
HAVE BEEN QUITE INFECTIOUS.
SHE'S BEEN ADMIRABLE,
ADORABLE AND ALTOGETHER AWESOME.
- OH, THAT'S GREAT,
BUT I'M REALLY HERE
TO SPEAK WITH TOJO.
- WHA-- ME?
- WELL, THIS MAY NOT
BE THE BEST PLACE
FOR THIS CONVERSATION.
LET'S GO
FIND A CAFE SOMEWHERE--
- WHOA WHOA WHOA!  WAIT, STOP.
SORRY, BUT LET'S HIT PAUSE
ON YOUR LITTLE TEA PARTY
WITH TOJO.
FIRST, THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE
HERE WHO'S BEEN DYING
TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
- JONAH?
- THANK YOU.
KASPER.
- HELLO, JONAH.
- I WANTED TO KNOW
HOW THOSE THREE
KIDS FROM THE BASE
ARE DOING SINCE COMING TO JAPAN.
- OBVIOUSLY
I COULD'VE TOLD HIM MYSELF,
TAKEN HIM TO SEE THEM EVEN.
BUT I FIGURED
IT MIGHT BE MORE MEANINGFUL
IF THE APPROPRIATE PERSON
DID THAT.
- VERY WELL.
I CAN TAKE YOU TO THEM.
ALAN, GET A RENTAL CAR FOR US,
WILL YOU?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
I'LL GET ONE RIGHT AWAY,
BUT LET US GO WITH YOU.
- I'M HAPPY TO DRIVE, SIR.
- THAT'S NOT NECESSARY.
IT'LL JUST BE THE TWO OF US.
- SO WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DO NOW?
- SIT IN A CAFE,
KILL SOME TIME.
- IS THIS OKAY?
- SURE, WHY NOT?
IT'LL GIVE THE GHOST
SOME TIME TO REALIZE
WHAT WE'VE DONE,
AND US A CHANCE TO RELAX.
- Kasper:
SHE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
SINCE THE DEAL WAS BETWEEN US,
IT DOES MAKE SENSE FOR ME
TO BE THE ONE TO SHOW YOU
HOW YOUR LITTLE ORPHAN FRIENDS
ARE DOING
IN THEIR NEW HOME HERE.
AND PLUS,
THIS MAY BE THE ONLY TIME
TWO JETSETTERS LIKE YOU AND I
ARE IN JAPAN TOGETHER.
WHICH COULD EXPLAIN WHY KOKO
WAS SO WILLING TO MEET ME HERE.
SO NOT IN A VERY TALKATIVE MOOD,
ARE YOU?
LOOK, I GET IT.
YOU HATE MY GUTS,
AND UNDERSTANDABLY.
BUT HEY,
I'M GETTING SLEEPY UP HERE.
ALL RIGHT,
GUESS I'LL TURN ON THE RADIO.
- I JUST CAN'T THINK
OF ANYTHING TO SAY RIGHT NOW.
AND EVEN IF I COULD, IT'S NOT
LIKE I'D TRUST A CREEP LIKE YOU.
- HMM.
NOW, JONAH, BE POLITE.
THAT'S MISTER CREEP TO YOU.
( laughs )
SEE THAT PLACE?
IT'S A TOP-NOTCH
INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL
WHERE YOUR OLD FRIENDS
MAURICE, ELINE AND
JANOT ARE ENROLLED.
IT GOES ALL THE WAY
FROM ELEMENTARY
THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL.
SATURDAY'S THEIR HALF DAY,
SO CLASS IS OVER ALREADY.
WE SHOULD SWING BY THEIR DORM.
MUST BE ON THEIR WAY BACK
FROM SCHOOL NOW.
RIGHT OVER THERE'S
WHERE THEY LIVE.
THEY'VE GOT A DORM MOTHER
WHO CAN BE A BIT STRICT,
BUT SHE KEEPS THEM FED
AND TAKES GREAT CARE OF THEM.
I WOULDN'T SAY THEY'RE RICH,
BUT THEY'RE BY NO MEANS POOR.
THESE KIDS ARE LEADING
PRETTY GOOD LIVES HERE.
WHAT'S THE HOLD-UP?
YOU GETTING OUT?
I THOUGHT
YOU WANTED TO SEE YOUR FRIENDS.
- THANKS, I'VE SEEN ENOUGH.
I KNOW YOU HAVE BUSINESS
TO TAKE CARE OF
WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
I'M SORRY
IF I'VE WASTED YOUR TIME.
- PLEASE, KID,
DON'T MENTION IT.
- SO MAYBE I CAN
TRUST YOU AFTER ALL,
LEAST A LITTLE.
- HA!
NEVER TRUST PEOPLE.
BUT FOR THE RECORD,
I DON'T LIE TO ANYONE
I'M TRYING TO WIN OVER
AND GET TO LIKE ME.
WHEN YOU QUIT
WORKING FOR KOKO,
WHY DON'T YOU COME
WORK FOR ME, JONAH?
- YEAH, NO,
THAT'S NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
- HEY, YOU NEVER
KNOW WHAT LIFE
MIGHT THROW YOUR WAY.
( laughs )
- WAIT FOR ME!
- EWW, GIRL COOTIES.
- ( radio playing )
- I HAD STATE POLICE
SEND ME THE CASE FILE.
THE BURGLARS TOOK ADVANTAGE
OF THE POWER OUTAGE TO BREAK IN.
LEAST THAT'S THEIR OPINION.
- Woman:
THANK YOU FOR ALL YOUR HELP.
I DO HOPE YOU'LL
CONTINUE
TO WORK WITH OUR
COMPANY IN THE FUTURE.
- GOOD LORD.
WE'RE NOT OBVIOUS.
LOOKS LIKE H.C.L.I.
RENTED OUT
THE WHOLE DAMN CAFE
OR SOMETHING.
- WELCOME BACK.
SO WHY DID YOU WANNA TALK?
- SEEMS I HAVE A NEW RIVAL.
H.Q. INTEL COULDN'T
TURN UP ANYTHING FOR ME,
SO I'M DIGGING MYSELF.
AFTER I ASKED YOU ALL
TO JOIN ME IN JAPAN,
I THOUGHT ABOUT
TOJO AND SUDDENLY
A LIGHT BULB WENT OFF.
TO BE HONEST,
I'M A LITTLE EMBARRASSED I
DIDN'T REALIZE IT EARLIER.
OUR COMPETITION
IS THE SECRET ARM
OF JAPAN'S DEFENSE
INTELLIGENCE HEADQUARTERS.
A SPECIAL RESEARCH UNIT
FOR THE FORMER JOINT STAFF,
ALSO KNOWN AS THE S.R. UNIT,
AND THEIR DIRECTOR
IS YOSUKE HINOKI.
IT'S YOUR OLD CREW, TOJO.
- ( theme music playing )
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS-- OH NO! ♪
♪ NO NO NO NO NO
NO NO NO NO NO NO NO ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪