- ( man vocalizing )
- Jormungand: I HAVE DEVOURED
FIVE CONTINENTS.
I HAVE SLURPED THREE OCEANS DRY.
THE VAST SKY ALONE REMAINS
OUT OF MY LONG REACH...
FOR I AM TRAPPED IN THIS BODY,
WHICH LACKS WINGS,
HANDS AND FEET.
I AM THE WORLD SERPENT.
I AM...
JORMUNGAND.
- ( theme music playing )
- MY PARENTS WERE KILLED BY A
FIGHTER JET JUST LIKE THAT ONE,
FULLY EQUIPPED
WITH THE LATEST TECHNOLOGY
AND A PAYLOAD OF LASER-GUIDED
SMART BOMBS.
THE PEOPLE WHO INVENT WEAPONS,
WHO CONSTRUCT THEM,
WHO SELL THEM,
WHO USE THEM...
I HATE THEM.
I WILL ALWAYS HATE THEM.
SO MAYBE
THIS IS GOD PLAYING
A TWISTED JOKE ON ME.
- STEP LIVELY, OFFICER JONAH.
LET'S GO.  ONE, TWO.
ONE, TWO.
RIGHT, LEFT.  RIGHT, LEFT.
- THIS IS KOKO HEKMATYAR,
A SELLER OF WEAPONS.
HERE I AM.
TRAVELING WITH AN ARMS DEALER.
- ALL OF MY SUBORDINATES
ARE HERE.
NOW THAT WE'VE ADDED YOU
TO THE RANKS,
THAT MAKES A TOTAL
OF NINE BODYGUARDS.
THEY'RE AN ODD BUNCH,
BUT I'M SURE YOU'LL BE FINE.
NORMALLY, I'D GIVE YOU MORE
OF A CHANCE TO SETTLE IN,
BUT WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THAT.
WE'VE GOT A BIT
OF A PROBLEM, YOU SEE,
WHICH IS THE REASON
WE'RE STUCK OUT HERE
IN THE HINTERLANDS
OF EASTERN EUROPE.
AND YOU ARE GOING TO HELP US
RESOLVE THIS PROBLEM.
THINK OF IT AS AN INITIATION
TO THE UNIT.
IT'LL GIVE US A CHANCE
TO ASSESS YOUR SKILLS.
MAO, WILEE.
- WHAT'S UP, BOSS?
AND WHO'S THE LITTLE KID?
- WHO, HIM?
EVERYONE, HI.
SAY HELLO TO JONAH.
- All:
HE'S THE NEW RECRUIT?
A CHILD SOLDIER?
AND HE'S ALREADY PACKING HEAT.
DAMN.
- NO NEED TO FREAK OUT, GUYS
NOW, TOJO, WILL YOU
EXPLAIN OUR PICKLE,
SO WE'RE ALL ON THE SAME PAGE?
- HASN'T REALLY CHANGED.
THE BASTARDS HAVE OUR CONTAINER
IMPOUNDED AT THE PORT.
THE CUSTOMS OFFICE WANT YOU
TO GIVE THEM A CALL.
MY GUESS IS THEY'RE GOING
TO DEMAND A HIGHER PRICE
THAN WHAT WE'D
ORIGINALLY AGREED TO.
THEY NEVER PLANNED ON LETTING
IT THROUGH IN THE FIRST PLACE.
YOU SEE THE SITUATION?
THE GOODS IN THAT CONTAINER
BELONG TO US,
AND WE NEED TO GET
THEM BACK, OKAY?
- I DON'T REALLY CARE
ABOUT THE BIG PICTURE.
ALL I NEED TO KNOW IS WHO
TO SHOOT AND WHERE THEY ARE.
SIMPLE AS THAT.
LEHM, VALMET,
PREPARE TO MOVE OUT.  HOP TO.
- Man: MISS HEKMATYAR,
I WONDER IF YOU UNDERSTAND
JUST HOW DEEPLY
THE CONTENTS
OF THAT CONTAINER OF YOURS
WILL AFFECT OUR COUNTRY.
I'M AFRAID CANNOT ALLOW IT
TO FALL INTO OUR
GOVERNMENT'S HANDS.
IF YOU INSIST UPON FORCING
THE ISSUE,
I'LL TAKE WHATEVER
MEASURES I MUST.
YOU DON'T WANT TO CROSS ME,
BITCH.
- FUNNY, I WAS GONNA SAY
THE SAME TO YOU.
- ( beeps )
- NOW THEN, JONAH,
WHAT DO YOU THINK
OF YOUR NEW TEAM?
- NOT A WHOLE LOT.
- A MAN OF FEW WORDS, HUH?
I DID A GOOD BIT OF RESEARCH
BEFORE TAKING YOU ON.
I KNOW WHERE YOU LIVED
AND WHERE YOU FOUGHT,
YOUR LIKES AND YOUR DISLIKES.
I ALSO KNOW WHY YOU GOT BOOTED
FROM YOUR LAST CREW.
YOU HATE WEAPONS.
DON'T YOU, JONAH?
CAN'T BE BOTHERED TO ANSWER?
- I'M NOT REALLY MUCH
OF A TALKER.
- I NOTICED, BUT THAT ISN'T
GOING TO CUT IT WITH THIS CREW.
- Lehm:
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK SO FAR?
- Valmet: WHAT, YOU MEAN
ABOUT THE NEW KID?
KIND OF HARD TO ANSWER THAT
QUESTION WHEN I'VE BARELY
EVEN HEARD HIM TALK.
HE'S HIDING SOMETHING.
HAVEN'T FIGURED OUT WHAT YET.
KOKO COULD BE IN DANGER.
I DON'T LIKE THE THOUGHT OF HER
ALONE IN A CAR WITH HIM.
SHE'S ALWAYS THIS WAY
WITH NEW RECRUITS.
JUST TOO EXCITED,
NO SENSE OF CAUTION.
ANYTHING HAPPENS TO HER
AND I'LL KILL THE KID MYSELF.
( coughs ) JEEZ, LEHM.
CAN'T YOU WAIT FOR YOUR NIC-FIX
TILL WE'RE OUT OF THE CAR?
I'M SUFFOCATING, HERE.
- YEAH, FINE.
- YOU ALWAYS DO THIS.  I'M GONNA
SMELL LIKE A FRIGGIN' ASHTRAY.
- KOKO.
- HE SPEAKS.  WHAT IS IT?
- I ASSUME THIS UNIT HAS
AN SOP FOR A TAIL.
- IF YOU SPOT 'EM,
THEN YOU GET TO SHOOT 'EM.
NO MERCY, HARD AND FAST.
- GOT AN ARMORED HOSTILE.
- OOH.
- Koko: JONAH!
HEY!  YOU HEAR ME?
WARN ME THE NEXT TIME YOU OPEN
FIRE ON A TARGET.
YOU SCARED THE CRAP
OUT OF ME.
- PRETTY SURE I JUST DID.
THOSE WERE JUST SCOUTS.
THE REAL FIREFIGHT'S
STILL COMING.
THERE'S A CONTAINER AT THE PORT
BELONGING TO KOKO HEKMATYAR.
SHE'S AN ARMS DEALER.
THE AIR FORCE CANNOT BE ALLOWED
TO GET THEIR HANDS
ON THAT SHIPMENT.
YOU WANT TO
KNOW WHAT'S INSIDE?
ENOUGH KITS TO UPGRADE
A FULL THREE SQUADRONS
OF OUR PRIMARY FIGHTER JETS.
WITH THOSE, OUR AERIAL FORCES
WOULD BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO CHALLENGE OUR NEIGHBORS.
THE BALANCE
OF POWER WOULD SHIFT.
IF THE MILITARY GETS
THOSE UPGRADE KITS,
YOU CAN BET YOUR ASS
THEY'LL USE THEM.
AND WE BOTH KNOW NOTHING
GOOD WILL COME OF IT.
I WANT THE POLICE KEPT OUT
OF THIS, UNDERSTOOD?
A FIREFIGHT?
YEAH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I SENT A SPECIAL UNIT IN
TO DEAL WITH HEKMATYAR'S PEOPLE.
IF THEY MAKE IT TO THE PORT,
THE SHOW'S OVER.  WE LOSE.
THAT'LL BE ALL.
- ( beeps )
- ( gunfire )
- THAT VAN'S GOT SOME
SERIOUS ARMOR.
IT MIGHT SUCK IF THEY TRY
AND COUNTERATTACK.
- AND IT'S BLOCKING
THE WHOLE DAMN ROAD.
- WE NEED TO GET TO KOKO.
THEY'LL HAVE HER PINNED IN
ON BOTH SIDES IF WE DON'T.
- THAT'S PROBABLY WHAT THEY'RE
GOING FOR.
- HANG ON.  HOW CLOSE DO YOU
THINK YOU CAN GET TO THAT VAN?
- YOU SERIOUS?
- HEY, KOKO,
COMING UP ON THE LEFT.
- GREAT.  MORE OF 'EM?
- WE WILL BE HAPPY TO GIVE YOU
RIDE TO PORT, LITTLE GIRL.
- VOSKHOD 6?
DAMN THAT OLD BUREAUCRAT.
LOOKS LIKE OUR
GUYS IN THE REAR
TOOK CARE OF THOSE
TRACKERS FOR US.
WE'RE PROBABLY STILL BEING
FOLLOWED, BUT HEY,
THEY'RE NOT SHOOTING
AT US ANYMORE.
DON'T THINK I DIDN'T NOTICE YOU
CALLING ME BY NAME EARLIER.
THAT'S TWICE NOW.  I LIKE IT.
I THINK WE'RE MAKING
REAL PROGRESS.  I HOPE YOU--
- KOKO.  KOKO.
- IS END OF ROAD FOR YOU.
BYE, BYE, ARMS DEALER BITCH.
- HOLD ON.
- THIS'LL BLOW 'EM SKY HIGH.
- ANTI-TANK MISSILE.
- A JAVELIN ATGM?
- ( laughs )
- WAS THAT A LAUGH?
HE'LL BE RELOADED
IN 20 SECONDS.
- HE CAN RELOAD,
BUT HE'S NOT GONNA FIRE.
- ALL UNITS, PULL BACK.
EVACUATE ALL PERSONNEL
IN THE HEWLETT BONDED AREA PORT.
- VOSKHOD 6, PULL BACK.
I REPEAT.
VOSKHOD 6, PULL BACK.
- THE MILITARY WILL
GET THEIR SHIPMENT
AND WE'LL BE HEADED FOR WAR.
I DID WHAT I COULD,
BUT IT'S OUT OF MY HANDS NOW.
- Koko: YOU HATE WEAPONS AS WELL
AS THEIR DEALERS,
YET HOW CAN YOU HOPE TO ACHIEVE
WHAT YOU WANT WITHOUT THEM?
LET'S SAY YOU KILLED ME.
THAT'S ONE NAME OFF YOUR LIST.
BUT WHAT, THEN?
YOUR JOB WOULDN'T BE DONE
UNTIL YOU TOOK OUT
THE REST OF MY TEAM.
THEY MAY NOT LOOK LIKE MUCH,
BUT THEY'RE REALLY
VERY GOOD AT WHAT THEY DO.
YOU COULDN'T KILL THEM
WITH YOUR BARE HANDS.
NO, YOU'D NEED A GUN.
YOU HATE YOUR WEAPON,
BUT CAN YOU GIVE IT UP?
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T.
YOU'LL SPEND THE REST OF YOUR
LIFE WITH A GUN IN YOUR HAND.
YOU MAY HATE WEAPONS
MORE THAN ANYONE,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
MATTER IN THE END
BECAUSE YOU ALSO KNOW BETTER
THAN ANYONE HOW USEFUL,
HOW NECESSARY THEY CAN BE.
DO YOURSELF A FAVOR
AND STICK WITH ME, OKAY?
I DEAL IN WEAPONS, JONAH.
I CAN SHOW YOU HOW TO LIVE
WITH YOUR HATE
WITHOUT GIVING UP YOUR GUN.
- WHY ARE YOU IN THE ARMS TRADE?
- FOR WORLD PEACE,
OF COURSE.
- WAKE UP, LITTLE GUY.
IT'S TIME FOR YOUR ROUNDS.
SWAP OUT WITH ME.
YOU'RE ON WITH OLD MAN LEHM.
( yawns )
WERE YOU ACTUALLY SLEEPING?
IT'S COLD, SO DRESS WARM.
I GOT TO CRASH.
- GOOD MORNING.
- HUH.
- ( gasps )
- THINK THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
I'VE HEARD YOU ASK A QUESTION.
LET'S SEE IF I GOT THIS RIGHT.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHY
A MAJORLY BADASS MERCENARY
WHO'S BEEN ON THE WINNING SIDE
OF A HUNDRED BATTLES WOULD WANT
TO TAKE A JOB AS A BODYGUARD
FOR A CHICK ARMS DEALER.
- I DON'T REMEMBER USING
THE WORD "BADASS."
- YOU'VE ONLY BEEN WITH THE CREW
FOR A FEW DAYS, SO I GET IT.
YOU'LL SEE SOON ENOUGH.
BUT WHY DID I TAKE THIS GIG?
'CAUSE IT'S FUN.
THAT'S MY REASON
FOR BEING HERE, ANYWAY.
THOUGH EACH MEMBER
OF THE UNIT HAS THEIR OWN.
GIVE IT SOME TIME AND
I THINK YOU'LL FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOUR REASON IS, TOO.
YOU'LL SEE WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE ONE OF US,
AND YOU'LL SEE THAT KOKO
IS ACTUALLY VERY--
SHE'S VERY... SPECIAL.
KOKO, BATHROOM'S BACK THAT WAY.
- ( growls )
WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY.
THREE HOURS AGO,
A TRANSPORT TEAM
CROSSED THE NORTHERN BORDER.
IF THE INTEL
I'VE GOT IS CORRECT,
THEY'RE CARRYING 15
MI-24D ATTACK HELICOPTERS,
ALSO KNOWN AS HIND Ds.
THE HELOS HAVE BEEN DISMANTLED
AND STUFFED IN WITH SPARE
PARTS FOR CONCEALMENT.
JUDGING BY THE TIMING,
IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY GOT WIND
OF OUR RECENT SUCCESS
AND DECIDED
THEY WANTED A PIECE
OF THE ACTION.
SO NOW THEY'RE
TRYING THEIR HAND AT IT.
I KNOW, STUFF LIKE THIS
HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
UNFORTUNATELY ( groans )
THE INFO ON THIS CONVOY
CAME DIRECTLY FROM HEADQUARTERS.
IF WE SCREW THIS UP,
IT'S GONNA COST US BIG.
( screams )
BIG, BIG, BIG!
- YOU SEE THE WAY SHE'S ROLLING
AROUND LIKE THAT?
IT MEANS THIS IS SERIOUS.
- WE NEED TO DEAL
WITH THIS TOUT DE SUITE.
FIRST, WE INTERCEPT
THEIR GOODS, BUT...
IF THEY PLAY HARDBALL,
WE MAY HAVE SOME
OBSTACLES TO ELIMINATE
SO TAKE A MOMENT TO PREPARE.
- OKAY.
- RIGHT.
YOU GUYS ARE PROS.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
TOJO, VALMET, YOU'LL NEGOTIATE
WITH NATIONAL DEFENSE.
LEHM, UGO, LUTZ, MAO, GET YOUR
GEAR.  YOU'LL BE MY BACKUP.
WILEE, R, STAY HERE AND HANDLE
COMMUNICATIONS WITH THE BRASS.
JONAH, YOU'RE WITH ME.
LET'S GO.
YEAH, KOKO HEKMATYAR HERE.
WE HAVE A CODE ORANGE.
I REPEAT,
CODE ORANGE.
- Man: RIGHT. DA.
DID YOU SEE ABOUT
CANCELING THE MOVERS?
- Man #2: DA, MR. KLOSHKIN.
- GOOD.
WELL, IN THAT CASE,
YOU CAN GO HOME.
GOOD JOB TODAY. ( sighs )
- Valmet: C. K. KLOSHKIN?
- Tojo: YEAH, AN ARMS DEALER.
HE'S A FREELANCER BASED
IN EUROPE,
BUT WORD HAS IT HE USED TO BE
IN THE INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY.
I'M ALMOST POSITIVE
HE'S OUR GUY.
- DID YOU TELL KOKO
THAT HE'S A FORMER SPOOK?
SHE COULD GET HURT.
YOU KNOW HOW DANGEROUS
THAT TYPE OF DUDE CAN BE.
- I DIDN'T HAVE TO.
SHE ALREADY KNEW.
BESIDES, SHE AND JONAH HAVE
FIVE GUYS BACKING THEM UP.
COME ON, CHIEF, IF YOU'RE
GONNA WORRY ABOUT ANYBODY,
IT SHOULD BE ME.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
I KNOW YOU CAN TAKE CARE
OF YOURSELF IN A FIGHT.
KOKO'S THE ONLY ONE I'D
EVER RISK MY LIFE FOR.
- SERIOUSLY, BUT WHAT
IF WE WERE UP AGAINST,
LIKE, THOSE AGENT GUYS
IN "THE MATRIX"?
- I'D WISH YOU LUCK AND GET
THE HELL OUT. ( snickers )
- HERE, JONAH, TAKE THIS.
- I HAVE MY OWN.
- I KNOW, IT'S A SPARE.
I'VE HEARD SOME RUMORS
AND GOTTEN MORE INTEL FROM HQ.
THIS GUY IS NO PRINCE.
NOT THAT MANY PEOPLE
IN THIS BUSINESS ARE.
- HELL, YEAH.
- WHAT'S THAT?
SHE SAID "GOOD HUNTING."
- IT'S BEEN FAR TOO LONG.
- HUNTING TIME.
- BOSS CAN BE EXTREME SOMETIMES,
AND I LIKE IT.
- Koko: FOR THE PURPOSES OF THIS
MEETING, YOU'RE NOT A SOLDIER.
LET ME SEE HERE.
THAT'S IT.
YOU'LL BE MY LITTLE BROTHER.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS, KEEP UP
THE ACT TILL I GIVE THE SIGNAL.
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU, MR. KLOSHKIN.
I'M KOKO HEKMATYAR.
- YES, MISS HEKMATYAR OF HCLI.
I'VE HEARD OF YOU.  FORGIVE THE
MESS, BUT I'VE JUST MOVED IN.
I'M AFRAID I DO NOT EVEN
HAVE A CARD TO GIVE YOU.
PLEASE, TAKE A SEAT.
I'LL BRING COFFEE.
PERHAPS THE BOY WOULD
LIKE A SODA.
AND WHO IS THIS YOUNG
FELLOW ANYWAYS?
AH, YOUR LITTLE BROTHER, YES.
( laughs ) WELL, I THINK
I HAVE A FAIRLY GOOD IDEA
WHY YOU'RE HERE.
LET'S TALK.
- Man: YOU'RE ASKING ME
TO CANCEL THE DELIVERY
OF THE HINDS.
THAT WOULD CERTAINLY
BE DIFFICULT,
THOUGH I WON'T
SAY IMPOSSIBLE.
EVEN AN OLD
MILITARY MAN LIKE ME
CAN LEAN TOWARD
THE SIDE OF THE DOVE.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, THOUGH,
THE RECENT DEAL THAT YOUR BOSS
MADE HAS US THINKING SERIOUSLY
ABOUT UPDATING OUR FULCRUMS.
- PLEASE ALLOW ME TO CONFER
WITH MISS HEKMATYAR.
- EXCELLENT.  SOUNDS LIKE
HE'S TAKING THE BAIT JUST FINE.
PLAY THE ANTI-AIRCRAFT
MISSILE CARD NEXT.
- ( beeps )
- SO SORRY.
- THAT'S YOUR TACTIC?
IT'S NOT VERY PROFESSIONAL
PLUNGING INTO A BIDDING WAR
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
YOU CAN'T EVEN BE BOTHERED
TO SHOW COMMON COURTESY
TO A FELLOW DEALER IN ARMS?
- AFRAID NOT.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED, YOU
HAVEN'T EARNED ANY COURTESY.
THIS IS HOW I SEE THE SITUATION,
MR. KLOSHKIN.
I HAD A PASTURE FULL OF COWS.
THEN YOU CAME ALONG AND TRIED
TO SLIP ONE OF YOUR COWS IN
TO BE RAISED WITH MY HERD.
- ( phone beeps )
- IT'S ME.
- SO NOW YOU WANNA SNEAK IN
TO GET YOUR COW BACK.
NOT MY FAULT IF YOU GET SHOT
IN THE ATTEMPT.
JONAH!
- BETTER LISTEN TO HER, KID.
NOTHING GOOD WILL COME
FROM SHOOTING ME.
SO MY INTEL WAS RIGHT.
YOU'VE GOT A CHILD SOLDIER
ON YOUR PAYROLL.
YOU MIGHT ACTUALLY BE A BIGGER
PIECE OF SHIT THAN I AM.
LOOK HOW TOUGH SHE IS.  I KNOW
FULL WELL THAT YOU'VE GOT A TEAM
OF HIRED GUNS AT YOUR DISPOSAL,
BUT DON'T PULL ANY STUNTS.
IF YOU DO, MY SNIPERS WILL
HAPPILY BLAST YOUR HEAD OFF.
HMM.  WOULD YOU LOOK
AT THE TIME?
YOU'RE WELCOME TO LEAVE.
DELIVERY OF THE HINDS
IS RIGHT ON SCHEDULE.
I HOPE IN THE FUTURE WE
CAN WORK MORE AMIABLY TO--
- ( laughs )
YOU REALLY ARE STUPID.
- HUH?
- MY EYES.
GIVE 'EM A GOOD LOOK.
GO ON, TAKE A NICE LONG LOOK.
STARE HARD ENOUGH, AND YOU'LL
SEE YOUR OWN REFLECTION,
BUT HERE'S THE THING,
I DON'T SEE YOU.
WE DEAL IN ARMS,
BUT THERE'S MORE
TO WHAT WE DO THAN COLD STEEL.
OUR REAL BUSINESS IS WITH
THE PEOPLE BEHIND THE WEAPONS.
- THE FUCK ARE YOU
RANTING ABOUT?
- I'M GLAD CELLS ARE WATERPROOF
THESE DAYS.
- WATCH IT.
I ALREADY WARNED YOU ONCE--
- YOUR SNIPERS?
WHY DON'T YOU CALL THEM?
- HEY, LEHM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD I TAKE THE SHOT?
- I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
HELLO.
ANYBODY THERE?
- YEAH, BOSS LADY.  WE'RE GOOD,
LOOKS LIKE WE GOT THEM ALL.
- EXCELLENT WORK.  PULL BACK
TO THE RENDEZVOUS POINT.
- ( beeps )
- ONE MORE CALL.
RIGHT NOW, YOUR LIFE IS WORTH
A SINGLE SHEET OF PAPER.
- Tojo: THAT'S RIGHT.
TWO LINES STRAIGHT THROUGH,
AND THEN SIGN BELOW
TO SHOW YOU MADE THE CHANGES.
DONE.
THE HINDS ARE NOW CONTRABAND.
KLOSHKIN'S CONTRACT
IS CANCELLED,
AND HAS JUST LEFT
THE COLONEL'S HANDS.
- ( gasps )
- BANG.
- KOKO.
NOT TOO BAD.  IT ISN'T DEEP.
HEAD WOUNDS JUST BLEED A LOT
YOU GOT LUCKY THIS TIME.
- WE'RE ALL DONE HERE.
LET'S GO HOME NOW.
- Jonah: SO THIS IS WHAT ARMS
DEALERS ARE LIKE.
THEY'RE NOT AT ALL
WHAT I EXPECTED.
BUT I THINK I'LL STICK
WITH THEM.
HERE I AM TRAVELING
WITH AN ARMS DEALER.
- Koko: WE'LL MEET WITH VALMET
AND TOJO IN THE NEXT TOWN OVER.
WE LEAVE AT 9:00.
- WHAT DID YOU THINK ABOUT
WORKING WITH THE BOSS?
- I LET HER GET HURT.
- WASN'T THAT PART OF THE PLAN?
DON'T SWEAT IT, KID.  YOU WERE
FOLLOWING KOKO'S ORDERS.
MAYBE IF YOU STOP WORRYING,
YOU'LL GET THE FOOD DONE FASTER.
WE'RE STARVING HERE.
- All:
A HUNGRY BELLY IS HUNGRY.
- THIS IS A VERY SIGNIFICANT
MOMENT FOR YOU, JONAH.
WITH THIS MEAL, WE MARK YOUR
OFFICIAL INITIATION
INTO THE CREW.  FROM NOW ON,
YOU'RE PART OF A FAMILY.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO GET USED TO
HAVING A TEAM YOU CAN RELY ON.
- ( groaning )
- NEVER GETS MEAL DUTY AGAIN.
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,  SHE IS
LOCO,  I SAID, "OH, NO" ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS
LOCO, I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪