- Jonah: I'VE WATCHED
EVERY DAY FOR TWO YEARS,
WAITING FOR KOKO
TO THROW THE SWITCH,
BUT SHE HASN'T.
JORMUNGAND'S STILL A DREAM
AND THE SKY'S STILL
OPEN FOR BUSINESS.
AND JUST LIKE KOKO WARNED US,
THE LAND AND THE SEA
HAVE BEEN SET ON FIRE.
WATER, FOOD, MONEY,
TERRITORY, RACE, RELIGION...
THE FIGHTING STARTED
FOR ALL SORTS OF REASONS.
KASPER KEEPS SAYING WE'RE
ON THE BRINK OF WORLD WAR III.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE
WHAT KOKO WOULD SAY.
- SEE, JONAH, 700,000 LIVES
GONE IN THE BLINK OF AN EYE.
- ( phone beeping )
- YO!
SEEMS LIKE THE WHOLE WORLD'S
COOKING NICE AND HOT, ISN'T IT?
YOU RAKING IN THE DOUGH?
- Koko: YOU REALLY
HAVE TO ASK?
- HAHA!
- ( theme music plays )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kasper: HONESTLY,
THE ARAB PENINSULA
HAS BECOME TOO STICKY
WHAT WITH PLUNGING THEMSELVES
INTO THE SIXTH
MIDDLE EASTERN WAR.
ONLY ONES MAKING MONEY THERE
ARE YOUNG DEALERS
WILLING TO RISK
THEY CAN GET OUT FAST.
SO, HOW IS IT
IN NORTH AFRICA?
- Koko: IF YOU BEELINE
FROM SOMALIA TO MAURITANIA,
YOU'LL BE IN DANGER
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
ULTIMATELY, EVERY
"SUCH-AND-SUCH SPRING"
UPRISING FAILED.
AT LEAST THEY
DON'T HAVE DICTATORS,
BUT THEY SURE AS HELL
DON'T HAVE PEACE.
HOW ABOUT SOUTHEAST ASIA?
- I HAD GREAT CUSTOMERS
IN INDONESIA,
BUT IT'S WAY
TOO HOT FOR ME NOW.
SINCE THEY GOT A NEW
ADMINISTRATION TWO YEARS AGO,
ONE MORE STATE JOINED
THE INDEPENDENCE MOVEMENT,
BUT FIVE VANISHED.
AND ALL THE LEADERS
WERE EXECUTED.
MEANWHILE, FRICTION WITH
THE CHINESE IMMIGRANTS
KEEPS GETTING WORSE,
TERRORISTS SET OFF
BOMBS EVERY DAY.
WITH ALL THE CHAOS,
THE STRAIGHT OF MALACCA'S
BEEN CLOSED
TO AMERICAN SHIPS.
SPEAKING OF TERRORISTS,
I HEAR LONDON LOST BIG BEN.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING
IT BLEW SKY-HIGH.
- Koko: ACTUALLY, THE OPPOSITE.
THEY TOPPLED IT.
COMPLETELY
DISINTEGRATED ITS BASE.
ALL THE COUNTRIES
IN THE OLD EURO-ZONE
HAVE BECOME NESTS
FOR TERRORIST GROUPS.
THE LOWER CLASSES ARE TARGETING
CIVIL SERVANTS NOW.
- Kasper: SOUNDS LIKE
A CIVIL WAR BREWING.
AT LEAST
IT'S NOT SOUTH AMERICA.
THEY'VE GOT CIVIL WAR
DOWN TO AN ART FORM.
THANKS TO DRUG CARTELS AND
THE RIGHT-WING GUERRILLAS,
ATTACKS THERE ARE AS ROUTINE
AS DRIVING A CAR.
- Koko: IT'S A SIMILAR STORY
IN EAST AND WEST AFRICA.
THEY'RE FIGHTING OVER WATER
IN THE EAST
AND MINERAL MINES
IN THE WEST.
ALTHOUGH THE REASONS THEY GIVE
TO RALLY THE TROOPS
ARE NEVER THAT
STRAIGHTFORWARD, OF COURSE.
- Kasper: NATURALLY.
AMIDST ALL THAT,
AMERICA AND THE NEW SOVIET UNION
HAVE GOTTEN BACK TO THEIR
OLD PRECARIOUS BALANCING ACT.
AND POLAND HAS SHUT DOWN
THEIR MISSILE DEFENSES.
- Koko: THE NEW SOVIET UNION--
( laughs )
BECAUSE THE COLD WAR WAS
SO MUCH FUN THE FIRST TIME.
ANYWAY, I HEARD YOU'RE ON BOARD
A SHIP IN THE SEVENTH FLEET.
AREN'T THEY GETTING READY
TO AIR RAID INDIA?
- JUST A LITTLE HEAT
TO KEEP PEOPLE HONEST.
THE FAR EAST
IS IN NO SHAPE FOR WAR.
THE YUAN'S WORTH ABOUT
AS MUCH AS TOILET PAPER,
SO THE CHINESE FEDERATION
IS TOO BUSY WITH THEIR ECONOMY.
AND UNITED HONG KONG STILL
DOESN'T EVEN HAVE A PRESIDENT.
BUSINESSES IN JAPAN ARE
ON THE EDGE OF A CLIFF, TOO.
DEPENDING ON WHETHER
THEY BUILT FACTORIES
IN THE SOUTH OR NORTH,
THEY'RE EITHER IN HEAVEN
OR THE PITS OF HELL.
SPEAKING OF, HAS THAT
COMPANY YOU SAVED
WITH NEW STOCK SURVIVED?
KISARAGI PHOTOCHEMICAL
ENGINEERING, RIGHT?
- THEY DIDN'T BUILD
ANY FACTORIES ABROAD,
SO THEY'RE DOING FINE.
- YOU DON'T SAY?
NOW, TELL ME,
WHEN DO I GET TO SEE
THIS NEW WORLD YOU'VE BEEN
SO CAREFULLY PLANNING.
YOU'VE BEEN BUSY, KOKO.
- OH, YOU NOTICED.
( laughs )
- I'VE BEEN WORKING IN
THIS BUSINESS FOR A LONG TIME.
I CAN USUALLY TELL
WHAT SOMEONE'S THINKING
JUST BY READING THEIR FACE.
SO, IN DEFENSE OF
THE KID'S HONOR,
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT HE NEVER TOLD ME
WHY HE LEFT YOUR TEAM.
NOT ONE WORD THE WHOLE TIME.
- WHY ARE YOU SAYING
IT LIKE THAT?
JONAH'S STILL WITH YOU, RIGHT?
- WELL, FOR NOW, YEAH.
BUT LIKE I SAID,
I CAN READ FACES.
JONAH'S GONNA QUIT.
COULD BE AS SOON AS TODAY.
HE'S A HIGHLY
SKILLED OPERATIVE,
SO LOSING HIM IS GONNA HURT.
YOU KNOW HOW HE IS.
HE HASN'T COMPLAINED ONCE.
BUT I CAN TELL HIS
FRUSTRATION'S BEEN BUILDING.
HE DOESN'T AGREE
WITH MY METHODS.
- MARATHON PHONE CALL.
- OBVIOUSLY, THAT'S NO SURPRISE.
- STOP IT.
- OH, RELAX.
- Koko: SO, HOW DID
YOU FIGURE OUT MY PLAN?
- ABOUT TWO YEARS AGO,
SCARECROW STARTED PESTERING ME.
- ( whimpering )
- WHAT ARE YOU AND
YOUR DAMN SISTER
PLANNING THIS TIME, HUH?
MY BOSS SEALED KOKO'S FILES!
HE WON'T TELL ME ANYTHING!
WHY, KASPER?
- ( thudding )
- ( grunts, coughs )
- I'M IN THE DARK.
I'D SAY YOU SHOULD
ASK KOKO.
- Scarecrow: SHUT UP!
OR SO HELP ME,
I WILL THROW YOU
IN THE SLAMMER!
- IF I WAS IN THE DARK,
THEN I KNEW
YOU WEREN'T ACTING
UNDER H.C.L.I's DIRECTION.
ALSO, JONAH QUIT
WORKING FOR YOU.
AND WHATEVER YOU WERE DOING
WAS BIG ENOUGH
TO MAKE THE HEADS
OF THE C.I.A. CLAM UP.
THOSE WERE THE PIECES.
I JUST HAD TO
ASSEMBLE THE PUZZLE.
- YOU KNOW I'M NOT
GONNA TALK ABOUT IT
ON A SATELLITE PHONE.
- OH, SO I DID
CONNECT THE DOTS!
AND THAT'S WHY YOU CHOSE ME
FOR YOUR NEXT MISSION.
ME AND MY TEAM
PROTECTING BABY SISTER.
- ( gasps )
- I UNDERSTAND.
WE'RE HEADING THERE NOW.
- UH...
- YUP, YOU HEARD ME.
WE'LL TALK LATER, KID.
LET'S MOVE.
CALL IN THE TEAM.
IT'S LOOKING NASTY.
- IT'S THE SAFEST LAUNCH SITE
WE COULD GET.
ALL WE CAN DO
IS HOPE A STRAY ROUND
DOESN'T HIT THE ROCKET.
TUCKED INSIDE THAT
BABY'S PAYLOAD FAIRING
IS A HIGHLY SOPHISTICATED
QUANTUM COMPUTER.
IT'S JORMUNGAND'S SECOND BRAIN.
- OH, THE MIDGARD SERPENT.
- Woman: T-MINUS 20 SECONDS.
19...
- OUR GLOBAL NETWORK
18...
- OF INFORMATION--
- 17...
- IT CAN ALL BE CONTROLLED
-  16, 15...
-BY A SATELLITE IN SPACE--
SAFE FROM HUMAN INTERFERENCE.
- SECOND SEQUENCE.
- THAT'S WHY IT'S FLAWLESS--
- SUPERCHARGER CABLES LINKED.
- BECAUSE NO ONE
CAN GET IN ITS WAY.
- TEN, NINE, EIGHT...
- TELL YOU WHAT, KASPER.
I'LL GIVE YOU THE SHORT VERSION.
- BLENDED FUEL ENGAGED
IN PRE-FLAME REACTION.
HYDROGEN PEROXIDE
INJECTED INTO GENERATOR.
THREE, TWO, ONE...
LIFT OFF.
- ( engine roars )
- BLAST OFF! YEAH!
- ( both cheer )
- ( laughing )
- Leila: GOOD SHOW, EVERYONE.
- Minami: YOU MUST
BE THRILLED, KOKO.
- ( sighs ) SUCCESSFUL LAUNCH.
THAT'S QUITE A RELIEF.
- WOW, THE JORMUNGAND
I SHRUNK DOWN IS IN SPACE.
ASTOUNDING.
- WOW! I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M SEEING THIS!
( giggles )
LOOK, BABS, SHE'S CRYING.
MISS STONE-COLD LEILA IS CRYING.
NOT SO TOUGH AFTER ALL.
- I SUPPOSE NOT.
- SINCE WHEN AM I STONE COLD?
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
TO AGREE WITH HER, BABSIE.
- Koko: IT'S SAID JORMUNGAND
ONCE ENCIRCLED THE EARTH,
BLOCKING THE LIGHT
OF THE SUN AND THE STARS
AND FORCING THE LAND
TO SINK INTO THE SEAS.
HOW WILL JORMUNGAND
CHANGE THE WORLD THIS TIME,
NOW THAT IT
CONTROLS THE SKY?
- ( laughs )
YEAH, WHO THE HELL KNOWS?
LET'S SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
WHAT? YOU THOUGHT YOUR PLAN
WOULD UPSET ME?
OBVIOUSLY, IT'S GONNA
DEAL A HEAVY BLOW TO
H.C.L.I. IN THE SHORT TERM.
AND THE GLOBAL GRID
COULD BE WIPED OUT ENTIRELY,
BUT IN THE LONG TERM,
PROFITS WILL ONLY GO UP.
IF YOU SHUT DOWN THE SKIES,
WE'LL BE LIMITED TO
LAND AND WATER DISTRIBUTION.
THAT'S WHAT THE COMPANY
WAS FOUNDED ON.
FLOYD WILL BITCH
AND MOAN FOR A WHILE,
BUT IN THE END,
HE'LL BE HAPPY.
I WON'T TELL HIM THAT,
OF COURSE.
IT WOULDN'T BE FUN.
DO YOU REALLY BELIEVE
OUR WORLD
WILL EVER BE FREE
OF WEAPONS, KOKO?
COME ON.
IF I DON'T HAVE
AERIAL WEAPONS,
I'LL SELL NAVAL ONES.
IF I DIDN'T HAVE BATTLESHIPS,
I'D SELL TANKS.
I'D SELL FIREARMS. I'D SELL LONG
SWORDS. I'D SELL HATCHETS.
YOU COULD RID THE WORLD OF IRON
AND I'D SELL WOODEN CLUBS.
THERE IS ALWAYS
A BIGGER STICK.
- HM-HMM.
- Kasper: AFTER ALL THAT TALK,
SHE LEAVES ON A PLANE.
( snickers )
- WHAT'S THAT?
- NOTHING.
JUST THINKING OUT LOUD.
GUESS SHE WON'T
BE ACTIVATING IT JUST YET.
- EXCUSE ME, KASPER.
WOULD YOU MIND
PULLING OVER FOR A MINUTE?
I'M GRATEFUL
FOR ALL YOU'VE DONE,
BUT I'M LEAVING.
THIS IS FINE.
CAN YOU
LET ME OUT HERE?
YOU'VE BEEN
A GOOD EMPLOYER, REALLY.
I HAVE NO COMPLAINTS,
BUT I'VE MADE UP MY MIND.
- WAIT, THAT'S CRAZY TALK.
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- POE, STOP THE CAR, WOULD YOU?
- Poe: YES, SIR.
ALAN, WE'RE STOPPING.
- Alan: TEN-FOUR.
- YOU'VE GOT A LOT TO LEARN
ABOUT BUSINESS, JONAH.
YOU DON'T JUST SAY
YOU QUIT AND WALK.
TWO WEEKS NOTICE
IS THE STANDARD.
BUT TO BE FAIR,
IT'S HARDLY ACCEPTED PRACTICE
TO EMPLOY MINORS
AS ARMED SECURITY.
AM I RIGHT?
IF SOMEONE CHARGED
ME WITH VIOLATING
CHILD LABOR LAWS,
I'D BE UP THE PROVERBIAL CREEK.
I FIGURED OUT A LONG TIME AGO
IF YOU EVER QUIT,
I COULDN'T STOP YOU.
SO THAT'S HOW
IT'S GONNA PLAY OUT.
FACT IS, IN A STRANGE WAY,
YOU AND I ARE EQUALS.
- WE'RE WHAT?
- YOUR SKILLS AS A SOLDIER
AND MINE AS AN ARMS DEALER
MAKE US EQUALLY STRONG.
AND THAT MEANS I HAVE
TO HANDLE YOU CAREFULLY.
YOU SEE, FOR MY OWN SAKE.
YOU ALSO KNOW
A DANGEROUS AMOUNT
ABOUT HOW
I CONDUCT MY BUSINESS.
I'M GONNA NEED YOU
TO STAY QUIET ABOUT THAT.
- I'M NOT A TALKER.
- GOOD.
- NOW ON TO THE MATTER OF
THE THREE ORPHAN KIDS
IN JAPAN.
- WHAT ABOUT THOSE KIDS?
- Poe: SHOULD'VE KNOWN
KASPER WOULD
BRING UP THE KIDS LIKE THIS.
HE'S TELLING JONAH
WHAT'LL HAPPEN
IF ANY SECRETS GET OUT.
- THE TWO OF US WILL
SUPPORT THEM TOGETHER,
TILL THEY'RE OLD ENOUGH
FOR COLLEGE.
THEY'LL GET ONE SHOT
AT THEIR ENTRANCE EXAMS.
HOW'S THAT SOUND?
- THANKS, KASPER.
- ( laughs )
DON'T THANK ME!
LIKE I SAID,
YOU ARE SHELLING OUT
HALF OF IT YOURSELF.
BUT DON'T WORRY.
EVEN MINUS THAT,
YOU'RE STILL PRETTY RICH.
THESE ARE YOUR SWISS
BANK ACCOUNT PAPERS
AND YOUR PASSPORT.
THESE ARE CRITICAL
FOR YOUR NEW LIFE, JONAH.
DON'T LOSE 'EM.
YOU WORKED OUT BETTER
THAN I EVER WOULD HAVE GUESSED.
THE CHILD SOLDIER
WITH A HEART OF GOLD.
- HUH? WHAT THE--
- ( door closes )
- ( gun cocks )
- WHY DID I TAKE MY GUNS?
KASPER SHOULD HAVE
SAID SOMETHING.
- Chequita: KASPER!
( growls )
- AH!
KNOCK IT OFF, CHEQUITA!
THIS CAN'T BE VERY GOOD
FOR MY SPINE.
AND LIKE I TOLD JONAH,
IT WAS THE BEST OPTION I HAD.
IT'S UNUSUAL FOR YOU
TO GET THIS UPSET ABOUT STUFF.
YOU MUST HAVE REALLY TAKEN
A LIKING TO HIM OR AM I WRONG?
- OF COURSE I DID!
HE WAS SO STRONG AND SO CUTE!
- SHEESH, SHE ACTS AS IF
SHE JUST LOST HER FAVORITE PET.
- DAMN IT, JONAH,
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
AND WHERE WILL YOU GO?
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO BE ALONE.
- YOU'LL SEE HIM AGAIN.
EVEN I FEEL SORRY
FOR THE KID.
HE'S DEVELOPED A TASTE
FOR WEAPONS AT AN EARLY AGE.
HE TRIES TO REJECT THEM,
BUT CARRIES THEM
WITHOUT EVEN THINKING.
IT'S A BIG WORLD. WHEN
YOU PART WAYS WITH SOMEONE,
YOU MAY NEVER
SEE THEM AGAIN.
BUT FOR THOSE
WHO'VE TAKEN UP ARMS,
THE WORLD IS
A MUCH SMALLER PLACE.
AND IT'S ONLY
GONNA GET SMALLER NOW.
- ( grunts )
( gasping )
( shaky breathing )
( sighs )
I CAN'T.
NO.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
DO SOMETHING, KOKO!
- SURE THING, JONAH.
- ( music plays )
- ♪ IT'S IN MY WORDS ♪
♪ LIKE AN UNSENT LETTER ♪
♪ TO YOU... ♪
- ( wind rushing )
- ♪ SEE IT THROUGH IN A PHRASE ♪
♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ SEE, HERE'S YOUR RAINBOW... ♪
- ( humming )
- ( wind rushes )
- ( shivers )
THAT'S SOME WIND.
- ♪ COME IN PEACE ♪
♪ YOUR RAINBOW... ♪
- ( wind rushes )
- WHAT IS IT, MAURICE?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, IT'S NOTHING.
- ♪ IT'S LIKE KISSING
YOUR BABY'S NOSE ♪
♪ A SONG OF BRAHMS ONE NIGHT ♪
♪ LOST IN THE SMILE... ♪
- YOU SHOULD TAKE
A QUICK BREAK, MAGGIE.
- THANKS, DOCTOR,
BUT I'M FINE.
- ( wind rushes )
- HMM.
- ( Man and Woman speak
in foreign languages )
- ( dog barks )
- Man and Woman:
EACH DAY, WE ARE LOSING
33,000 CHILDREN
DUE TO STARVATION
AND LACK OF
MEDICAL ATTENTION.
( continues in
foreign languages )
- Schokolade: WE SHOULD
LET UP ON KASPER'S GROUP.
GO AFTER SOMEONE ELSE.
THOSE PEOPLE ARE NOTHING
BUT BAD NEWS.
- SHUT IT!
JUST HURRY UP AND FINISH
THAT DAMN BUG!
- Minami: KAREN! COME ON.
LET'S HIKE OUT
TO THOSE HILLS.
SUNSHINE! BUTTERFLIES!
- YOU KNOW WE CAN'T
DO THAT NOW.
MISS HEKMATYAR GAVE US
STRICT INSTRUCTIONS
TO STAY HERE
TILL IT'S DONE.
- ( wind rushes )
- ( speaking in foreign
languages continues )
- OKAY THEN,
HOW ABOUT MAHJONG?
WE'VE GOT ENOUGH PLAYERS.
- YES, DOCTOR,
THAT WOULD BE ACCEPTABLE.
- Man and Woman:
...IN 40 COUNTRIES IN THE WORLD,
OUT FIGHTING WITH WEAPONS
ARE YOUNG SOLDIERS
IN COMBATS.
- ♪ SING A SONG ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE SONG ♪
♪ SEE YOUR RAINBOW ♪
♪ IN THIS SONG ♪
♪ TO FORGIVE ♪
♪ TO LOVE YOURSELF ♪
♪ THE RAINBOW SAILS ♪
♪ WITH YOUR WISH ♪
♪ THROUGH THE STARRY SKY. ♪
- ( music ends )
- I HAVEN'T EATEN ANYTHING
IN TWO DAYS.
THAT MIGHT BE A RESTAURANT,
BUT I DON'T SPEAK
THE LANGUAGE HERE.
- Lutz: BOO!
( snickers )
YOU'VE SURVIVED WAR,
BUT YOU CAN'T GO
INTO A RESTAURANT ALONE?
- WHOA.  LUTZ?
- THAT'S RIGHT, KID.
IT'S ME.
JUST CALL ME
YOUR GUARDIAN ANGEL.
HERE'S A TRAVEL TIP.
THE INTERNATIONAL GESTURE
FOR FOOD,
LIKE THIS, SEE?
THEN GIVE THEM
A COUPLE OF DOLLARS.
IF IT'S NOT ENOUGH,
YOU GET TO WASH DISHES.
HEY, CHECK OUT WHAT
THE CAT DRAGGED IN.
- ( gasps )
YOU'RE ALL HERE?
- WE WERE NEARBY WHEN WE HEARD
YOU QUIT ON KASPER,
SO WE CAME TO GET YOU.
THOUGH IT'S YOUR
CHOICE, OF COURSE.
HONESTLY, THESE GUYS
HAVE BEEN A REAL PAIN IN MY ASS
WITHOUT YOU BEING AROUND.
WE COULD USE
ANOTHER DECENT HUMAN.
HOW ABOUT IT?
- YOU'RE HERE FOR ME?
- YOU'VE GROWN A LOT
IN THE LAST TWO YEARS, KID.
WHAT HAVE THEY BEEN
FEEDING YOU OVER THERE?
AS FOR ME, WELL,
I GUESS I JUST HAVEN'T HAD
THE SAME APPETITE WITHOUT YOU
BEING PART OF THE TEAM.
- THANKS, UGO.
- SEEMS YOU'VE
FALLEN BEHIND ON YOUR
LANGUAGE TRAINING, JONAH.
NOT MUCH FUN
WHEN YOU CAN'T
COMMUNICATE WITH
THE LOCALS, HUH?
I'M NOT TOTALLY FLUENT HERE,
BUT I KNOW ENOUGH TO GET BY.
IT'S BEEN BORING
THE LAST TWO YEARS
WITHOUT SOMEONE TO TEACH.
- HEY, WILEE.
- COME ON, GUYS,
WHAT THE CRAP?
NOBODY TOLD ME WE WERE
ALL GIVING MINI-SPEECHES.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
MAKE UP YOUR OWN MIND, JONAH.
BUT I WOULD LIKE YOU AROUND.
I'M BORED WITH TEASING LUTZ.
- YEAH, I BET.
- I TRIED MY BEST NOT
TO MAKE A BIG DEAL OF IT
WHEN YOU LEFT. I LIKE TO
KEEP THINGS PROFESSIONAL.
BUT THE TRUTH IS,
IT HASN'T BEEN THE SAME.
- HI, MAO.
- HEY, JONAH.
I NEVER DISCHARGED YOU,
SO TECHNICALLY
YOU'VE BEEN "AWOL"
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
- I'M IN TROUBLE.
- SO, YOU FINALLY GOT SICK
OF KASPER'S CRAP, HUH?
I ALWAYS KNEW
YOU'D COME BACK EVENTUALLY.
I TEND TO BECOME RATHER ATTACHED
TO MY COLLEAGUES
AND I DIDN'T LIKE
YOU BEING GONE.
NOW EAT UP, KID,
BEFORE YOU PASS OUT.
- THANKS, VALMET.
- Koko: ENOUGH, GUYS.
I'M GONNA CHOKE ON
ALL THIS KUMBAYA CRAP.
JONAH, DID YOU CROSS
THE CASPIAN SEA
ALL BY YOURSELF?
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
( chuckles )
HAVE A DRINK.
OFFICER JONAH, I WOULD SAY
YOU'VE EARNED IT.
- KOKO.
- I KNOW. IT'S
A TOUCHING REUNION,
BUT THERE'S
NO TIME TO WASTE.
THERE'S A REASON WE'RE
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD
AND THE TEAM'S GOT
THEIR HEAVY GEAR.
THIS IS DANGEROUS TERRITORY
AND IT COULD GO
FULL-ON WAR ZONE ANY MINUTE.
BAKU, AZERBAIJAN...
THE NEW SOVIET UNION
HAS THEIR HEARTS SET
ON THE OIL FIELDS HERE.
THEY'RE GATHERING
AT THE BORDER.
BUT I'M THE KIND OF WOMAN
WHO DELIVERS ON HER PROMISES.
TOOK SOME TIME, BUT JORMUNGAND
IS FINALLY COMPLETE.
I JUST HAVE TO SEND
THE ACTIVATION SIGNAL.
AND ONCE I DO,
I CAN PREVENT
THE NEW SOVIET ARMY
FROM INVADING.
YOU'VE HAD TWO WHOLE YEARS
TO THINK IT OVER, JONAH.
SO, WHAT'S THE VERDICT?
WHO'S MORE CRAZY,
ME OR THE WORLD?
- WILL ACTIVATING JORMUNGAND
REALLY BRING PEACE
TO THE WORLD?
- ( cackles )
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M NO FORTUNE-TELLER,
BUT I DO LIKE MY ODDS.
THE HEAVENS ARE
ABOUT TO EXPERIENCE
OVER A CENTURY
OF RETROGRESSION.
BUT WE'RE WIRED
TO MOVE FORWARD, NEVER BACK.
AND THE SKY THAT USED
TO SYMBOLIZE
ULTIMATE ACHIEVEMENT AND FREEDOM
WILL BE CLOSED TO US.
WHEN WE SEE THE DAWN
OR A SOARING BIRD,
WE'LL BE REMINDED OF WHAT
WE WERE TOO RECKLESS TO KEEP.
THE HUMILIATION OF HUMANITY
WILL CONSTANTLY
HANG OVER OUR HEADS.
DO YOU THINK THE HUMAN RACE
WILL KEEP FIGHTING THEN?
PERSONALLY, I DON'T
BELIEVE THEY WILL.
HUMANS CAN'T
STAND HUMILIATION.
THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT SEPARATES US FROM THE APES.
- BUT SHOULD I TRUST
YOUR INTUITION?
- WELL, I AM
A FORMER ARMS DEALER.
AND I DID GET YOU ALL
MIXED UP IN THIS TO BEGIN WITH.
- I THINK THAT BOTH YOU
AND THE WORLD ARE CRAZY.
THAT SAID, I'M TAKING
MY CHANCES WITH YOU.
- I'M GLAD.
THEN I'LL GIVE YOU
A FRONT-ROW SEAT, JONAH.
LOAD UP.
LET'S GO!
- ( rapping in French )
( rapping ends )
- AND SO IT WAS.
I TRAVELLED WITH
AN ARMS DEALER.
NOW, I WILL TRAVEL
A NEW WORLD
WITH KOKO HEKMATYAR.
- PROJECT JORMUNGAND,
ACTIVATE!
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS-- ♪
♪ OH NO, NO, NO, NO! ♪
♪ NO, NO, NO,
N-- N-- N-- NO ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪