- SO WHY'D YOU WANNA TALK?
- SEEMS I HAVE A NEW RIVAL.
H.Q. INTEL COULDN'T TURN UP
ANYTHING FOR ME,
SO I'M DIGGING MYSELF.
OUR COMPETITION
IS THE SECRET ARM
OF JAPAN'S DEFENSE
INTELLIGENCE HEADQUARTERS,
A SPECIAL RESEARCH UNIT
FOR THE FORMER JOINT STAFF,
ALSO KNOWN AS THE S.R. UNIT.
AND THEIR DIRECTOR
IS YOSUKE HINOKI.
IT'S YOUR OLD CREW, TOJO.
- ( theme music playing )
- Kasper:
'COURSE, YOU KNOW A LOT MORE
ABOUT THE D.I.H. THAN I DO.
SO THIS HINOKI ISN'T MUCH MORE
THAN A PHOTO TO ME.
I'VE GOT A STRONG SUSPICION
THEY'RE THE GHOSTS
WHO'VE BEEN HAUNTING ME
AND WHO'VE BEEN CAUSING
ALL KINDS OF TROUBLE
WITH MY OPERATIONS
IN SOUTHEAST ASIA.
BUT I'D LIKE CONFIRMATION.
YOU WERE AN S.R. OFFICER.
CAN YOU TELL ME IT'S THEM?
- THIS SOUNDS MORE LIKE A FAVOR
THAN A COMMAND, KASPER.
I'M CONFUSED.
- GRANTED, I USED TO BE
YOUR BOSS, TOJO,
BUT I DIDN'T COME HERE
TO EXPLOIT THAT.
I'VE JUST GOT A JOB.
AND YOU'RE THE BEST MAN
TO HANDLE IT.
ACTUALLY,
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE INTO THIS,
THE WAY YOU LIKE TO WORK.
YOU'D ALWAYS SAY
HOW YOU HATED MY METHODS,
AS YOU BOUNCED FROM JOB TO JOB,
WHEREVER THE WIND BLEW.
WELL, PAL, THINK OF THIS
AS A GENTLE SPRING BREEZE,
BLOWING YOU BACK TO OLD TIMES.
WE CAN NEVER TRULY ESCAPE
THE CHAINS OF OUR PAST, CAN WE?
- THIS DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
WHY ARE YOU TAKING
THE S.R. UNIT SO LIGHTLY?
YOU MAKE IT SOUND
LIKE THEY'RE AN EASY WIN.
KNOWING YOU, YOU ALREADY
PICKED A FIGHT WITH THEM
AND NOW YOU WANT US
TO DO THE CLEANUP.
WIPE YOUR OWN ASS.
- I DIDN'T PICK ANYTHING.
I'VE SIMPLY
ACCEPTED A CHALLENGE.
AN INVISIBLE MAN
TRIED TO STRANGLE ME,
SO I DID WHAT'S NATURAL--
I SWUNG MY FISTS.
AND IF I WAS TAKING
THIS LIGHTLY,
I WOULDN'T BE COMING TO YOU.
YOU CAN SAY
YOU DON'T LIKE IT, KOKO,
BUT I KNOW YOU'LL HELP.
- PLEASE.
"AN INVISIBLE MAN?"
IF YOU WANT TO DISCUSS BUSINESS,
THEN SPARE ME THE HYPERBOLE.
- SO LET'S SAY
I DO PROVE THEY'RE BEHIND THIS.
WHAT'RE YOU GONNA DO TO THEM?
- CRUSH THEM, OBVIOUSLY.
I'M HOPING YOU'LL MAKE
THESE GHOSTS EASIER TO SEE
WHEN IT'S TIME
FOR THE CROSSHAIRS.
- THERE HE IS.
THE MAN WHO LIVES
FOR DESTRUCTION.
YOU'LL NEVER CHANGE.
AND HE WON'T EITHER.
HINOKI'S AS STEADFAST
AS TWO TONS OF SOLID ROCK.
THIS OPERATION WON'T RUN
AS SMOOTHLY AS YOU THINK.
- ( laughs )
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
YOU MUST'VE BEEN A VERY TALENTED
OPERATIVE FOR THE S.R. UNIT.
BUT YOU'RE TRYING TO TELL ME
WHEN YOU LEFT,
THEY WEREN'T EVEN AFFECTED?
TRUE-- A MAN
CAN'T BE CHANGED SO EASILY.
BUT A GROUP
IS A DIFFERENT STORY.
THE AGENCY COLONEL
HINOKI IS WORKING
SO HARD TO KEEP STRONG.
MAY BE A CASTLE
BUILT OUT OF SAND.
- TALKS HIS HEAD OFF,
THEN JUMPS RIGHT
BACK ON A PLANE.
- THE S.R. UNIT'S STRONGHOLD.
IT'S AN OLD DUMMY CORPORATION
BASED IN JAKARTA.
KASPER WANTS TO GO THERE
TO DISTRACT THEM WHILE WE WORK.
- MM-HMM.
WE SIBLINGS
LOOK AFTER EACH OTHER.
HAVE EVER SINCE WE WERE LITTLE.
THAT'S HOW HE KNEW I'D HELP.
IF WE SUCCEED,
MY BROTHER CAN REGAIN HIS TRADE
ROUTES IN SOUTHEAST ASIA.
THE BOATLOAD OF CASH
HE PROMISED WON'T HURT, EITHER.
BUT THERE'S RISK.
YOU MAY HAVE TO FIGHT
AGAINST YOUR OLD TEAM AND BOSS.
YOU FEEL TORN ABOUT THAT?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
HEY, DON'T LOOK AT ME
LIKE I'M A HEARTLESS BASTARD.
'CAUSE I'M NOT.  LOOK,
I CAN'T DRIVE MYSELF CRAZY.
IT'S TRUE
HINOKI WAS MY MENTOR.
HE POUNDED ALL SORTS
OF INVALUABLE CRAP INTO MY SKULL
WHEN I WAS A YOUNG OFFICER.
I'LL NEVER FORGET THAT.
BUT I'M A PRO,
AND I WORK FOR YOU NOW.
IT'S JUST LIKE HINOKI
TAUGHT ME--
I CAN'T BEAT AN ELITE ADVERSARY
IF I LET FEELINGS GET INVOLVED.
BESIDES--
- NOBODY PUTS A MISERABLE LOOK
ON MY KOKO'S FACE!
- ( thinking ) MY NECK IS IN
HELL, BUT MY BACK'S IN HEAVEN.
WHAT A SLEEPER HOLD.
IT'S A BIG WORLD,
BUT KOKO'S UNIT
IS THE ONLY PLACE
I CAN EXPERIENCE
A MOVE LIKE THIS.
I'M SO LUCKY.
NO, WAIT, I CAN'T BREATHE.
UNCLE.  UNCLE!
I GIVE.
- OH, MAN.
TOJO REALLY PUT HIS FOOT
IN IT THIS TIME.
- Lehm: OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
WE STILL THE NEED GUY.
- ( vibrating )
- HMM.
DON'T RECOGNIZE THE NUMBER.
- Tojo: COLONEL HINOKI,
GOOD AFTERNOON.
I KNOW
THIS IS OUT OF THE BLUE,
BUT DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT
TO TALK?
IT'S AKIHIKO TOJO.
- HUH?
OH.  TOJO, WOW.
DIDN'T THINK
I'D HEAR YOUR VOICE TODAY.
IT'S BEEN AGES.
SO HOW ARE YOU?
I TAKE IT YOU'RE IN JAPAN?
HANG ON A MINUTE,
I'M DRIVING.
- OH, I'M SORRY.
I CAN CALL BACK LATER.
- NO, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMEWHERE
I CAN PULL OFF THIS STUPID
HIGHWAY FOR A MINUTE.
AH, SCREW IT,
I CAN TALK AND DRIVE.
I'VE DONE MORE DANGEROUS THINGS.
( laughs )
SO I GUESS THIS MEANS
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
- YUP, ALIVE AND KICKING.
I'M IN JAPAN FOR WORK.
SOUNDS LIKE
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED.
- DON'T CHANGE WHAT'S WORKING,
RIGHT?
I'M IN GOOD HEALTH.
THOUGH I HAVE REACHED THAT AGE
WHERE I START PONDERING
THE HEAVY SHIT
MORE THAN I'D LIKE. ( laughs )
SO WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
HEARD YOU QUIT WORKING FOR
KASPER AT H.C.L.I. A WHILE BACK.
YOU STILL USING THE SKILLS
I TAUGHT YA?
I'D HATE TO THINK
I WASTED MY TIME.
- NO WORRIES THERE.
I DID QUIT WORKING UNDER KASPER,
BUT I'M STILL WITH H.C.L.I.
THAT'S WHY I'M CALLING,
ACTUALLY.
- OH? THEN MAYBE
WE SHOULD CUT TO THE CHASE.
- I'D LIKE YOU
TO PULL OUT OF THE CONFLICT
CONCERNING KASPER'S
SOUTHEAST ASIAN TRADE ROUTE.
H.C.L.I. IS TAKING MEASURES
TO ELIMINATE THE S.R. UNIT.
- WELL,
ISN'T THAT INTERESTING?
AND HOW HAS KASPER
BEEN DESCRIBING US?
- HE'S CALLING YOU GHOSTS.
- THAT'S A PRETTY
DEAD-ON DESCRIPTION.
AN INVISIBLE FIST
LANDS THE MOST DAMAGING BLOW.
SO NOW YOU'VE GOT ME CURIOUS,
TOJO.
HOW DOES HE PLAN TO DEFEAT
A GHOST HE CAN'T SEE?
- WELL, A PERSON WHO'S SERVED
UNDER BOTH YOU AND KASPER
KNOWS HOW TO SEE THE GHOST.
THAT'S THE ROLE
I'VE BEEN GIVEN IN THIS DANCE.
- ( laughing ) HEY, IT'S NOISY
ON YOUR END. AT THE AIRPORT?
- I BEG YOUR PARDON?
- THIS CONVERSATION'S OVER.
WE MAY NEED TO TALK AGAIN,
SO HOLD ON
TO THAT PRE-PAID PHONE.
- ( phone clicks )
- PHEW.
- AW, JEEZ.
YOU ACTUALLY SAID "PHEW."
MOST PEOPLE JUST EXHALE, TOJO.
- DAMN IT!
DON'T EAVESDROP, YOU OLD FART.
- I FIGURED YOU'D MAKE A BREAK
FOR THE NEAREST EXIT
AFTER GETTING PUT
IN AN AWKWARD SPOT LIKE THIS.
- YEAH, LIKE I'D EVER RUN.
IT'S A JOB, NOTHING MORE.
- ( laughing )
- YOUR SENSE OF
HUMOR'S MESSED UP.
- ( Hinoki laughing )
POOR KID. HE ALWAYS REVEALS
A LITTLE TOO MUCH
WHEN HE'S ANXIOUS
ABOUT A MISSION.
THAT HASN'T CHANGED.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE HAD A GOOD LAUGH.
- Tojo: I FISHED AROUND.
LONG STORY SHORT, KOKO,
YOUR BROTHER'S RIGHT.
THE S.R. UNIT'S BEHIND THIS.
- THAT WAS SOME QUICK WORK.
WELL DONE.
FILL THE REST OF US IN
ON THE S.R. UNIT.
TRY AND KEEP IT SHORT AND SWEET
SO IT'S AT JONAH'S LEVEL.
- JONAH'S LEVEL?
( groans )
THEY'RE THE SELF-DEFENSE FORCE'S
SECRET TEAM.
MAIN FOCUS,
INTEL AND ESPIONAGE.
SIMPLY PUT, THEY'RE SPIES.
THEY WORKED
IN THE THICK OF THE COLD WAR
AT THE REQUEST OF THE D.I.A.--
AMERICA'S DEFENSE
INTELLIGENCE AGENCY.
HISTORICALLY
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN DIFFICULT
FOR INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES
TO OPERATE IN JAPAN.
THE POLICE FORCE
HAS ALL OF THE POLITICAL POWER.
AND THE GOVERNMENT
HAS NEVER PRODUCED
CONSISTENT
INTERNATIONAL POLICY.
NOTHING STABLE.
IT'S TOUGH TO DO YOUR JOB
WHEN YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT THE RULES ARE.
IN RECENT YEARS,
YOU COULD HARDLY CONSIDER
THE J.S.D.F.'S COUNTER
OR CENTRAL
INTELLIGENCE OPERATIONAL.
SINCE THE WAR, A NUMBER OF
AGENCIES HAVE SPRUNG UP,
BUT NONE OF THEM LASTED LONG.
THERE WAS ORGANIZATION F,
THE KAWABE AGENCY,
THE GROUND STAFF.
THEY ALL COLLAPSED.
VIETNAM
BROUGHT NEW OPPORTUNITY.
THERE WERE AREAS AMERICA
COULDN'T INFILTRATE,
BUT JAPAN COULD.
THE S.R. WAS ONE OF THE GROUPS
CREATED TO GATHER INTEL THERE.
THE ORIGINAL DIRECTOR
STATIONED THEIR BASE
IN JAKARTA, INDONESIA.
AND SELECTED 50 ELITE SOLDIERS
FROM THE ARMED FORCES
FOR HIS TEAM.
BUT LIKE THE GROUPS
BEFORE THEM,
THEY LACKED THE FUNDING
TO STAY AFLOAT.
AS A TOP-SECRET UNIT,
THEY COULDN'T EXACTLY MARCH
INTO THE MINISTRY OF FINANCE
AND DEMAND MORE MONEY.
SO THEY DEVISED A WAY
TO SUPPLEMENT THE S.R.'S BUDGET
BY MEDIATING ARMS DEALS
BETWEEN AMERICA AND THE J.S.D.F.
THE S.R. SET UP
A DUMMY CORPORATION,
GANVILLE TRADING,
AS THE FACE FOR THEIR DEALS.
EVEN AFTER VIETNAM,
THEY KEPT USING GANVILLE,
LIKE A PEA CRAB HIDING
IN ANOTHER CREATURE'S SHELL.
THEY THRIVED IN THE ARMS TRADE,
SEPARATE FROM JAPAN,
WHILE WAGING INFORMATION WARFARE
AGAINST COMMUNIST POWERS.
THEIR ARMS BUSINESS
WAS SO SUCCESSFUL,
THEIR S.R. BUDGET
BECAME UNNECESSARY.
THAT'S ABOUT THE TIME
THEY GOT THEIR FIFTH DIRECTOR,
COLONEL HINOKI,
MY OLD BOSS.
IN '97, THE D.I.H.,
JAPAN'S DEFENSE
INTELLIGENCE HEADQUARTERS,
UNDERWENT
SIGNIFICANT REORGANIZATION,
AND THE S.R. SLIPPED
EVEN DEEPER BETWEEN THE CRACKS.
WITH ITS BASE IN INDONESIA
AND ABILITY TO FUND ITSELF,
HIDING WASN'T HARD.
TODAY, ONLY A HANDFUL OF STAFF
AND ASSEMBLYMEN
EVEN KNOW IT EXISTS.
- ( yawns )
- IN SOUTHEAST ASIA'S
UNDERWORLD,
THE S.R. IS FREE TO EXERCISE ITS
OWN AUTHORITY IN IDEAL SECRECY.
WITH KASPER QUICKLY EXPANDING
H.C.L.I.'S INFLUENCE THERE,
CONFLICT WAS INEVITABLE.
AND NEITHER SIDE
WANTS TO BACK DOWN.
THE ECONOMIC, RELIGIOUS AND
CULTURAL TENSIONS IN THE REGION
CREATE A PERFECT CHAOS
FOR THE ARMS TRADE.
THERE'S SIMPLY TOO MUCH MONEY
AT STAKE.
- TELL US ABOUT HINOKI.
- HIS COVER IS THAT HE WORKS
AS THE SENIOR EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR
OF GANVILLE.
HE'S GOT A SHAM MARRIAGE
WITH SOME THAI WOMAN.
HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW HOW
HE KEEPS ALL HIS LIES STRAIGHT.
THE TRUTH-- HE'S A WARRIOR
WITH A LONG MILITARY CAREER
WHO FOUND HIS GREAT PASSION
IN ESPIONAGE.
STARTED YOUNG--
JAPANESE ARMY.
HE STUDIED
AT THEIR UNIVERSITY.
TRAINED AS A RANGER
WITH THE WESTERN ARMY INFANTRY,
THEN ENROLLED IN COMMAND SCHOOL
AND BECAME AN OFFICER
IN THE AMERICAN DEFENSE
INTELLIGENCE AGENCY.
HE WORKED HIS WAY
INTO THE S.R. UNIT,
AND QUICKLY
DISTINGUISHED HIMSELF THERE.
HE IMPRESSED THE AMERICANS
WHEN HE POSED
AS A JAPANESE BUSINESSMAN,
SMUGGLED HIMSELF
INTO AN IRANIAN FACTORY
FOR HIGHLY-ENRICHED URANIUM,
AND GATHERED INTEL
ON THEIR NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
HE WAS KNOWN AS
JAPAN'S ONE AND ONLY SPYMASTER.
WHEN IT COMES TO RUNNING
A SECRET UNIT,
HE'S OLD SCHOOL.
ONCE YOU'RE IN THE DARK,
YOU STAY THERE
AND DRAW YOUR TARGET
INTO THE SHADOWS.
HE'LL GO TO A LOT OF TROUBLE
TO KEEP THINGS NEAT AND QUIET.
AS I TOLD KOKO,
HE'S STEADFAST AS A ROCK,
AND WON'T DEVIATE
FROM HIS M.O.
HE WON'T ATTACK HEAD-ON.
SO WATCH YOUR BACK.
- SINCE WHEN DO I NOT?
SEEMS WE ACTUALLY
HAVE A LOT IN COMMON,
IT'S A SHAME
WE CAN'T GET ALONG.
OH, WELL, THAT'S LIFE.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M LOOKING
TO MAKE NEW FRIENDS OR ANYTHING.
OH!
HE'S ASLEEP.
JONAH'S ASLEEP STANDING UP!
- Valmet: TO BE FAIR,
I ALMOST NODDED OFF MYSELF.
- Lutz: YEAH. DUDE, HOW WAS THAT
THE SHORT AND SWEET VERSION?
- ( Tojo laughs )
- Man:
KUROSAKA, YOU'RE UP NEXT.
YOU HAVE A REPORT
FROM THE SCENE
OF THE KORWIT NUALKHAIR
INCIDENT?
- Kurosaka: THE ROBBERY
HAPPENED DURING A BLACKOUT,
CAUSED BY A TYPHOON.
THE TARGET AND THREE OTHERS
WERE SHOT--
ONCE IN THE HEAD,
TWICE IN THE HEART.
I SAW PHOTOS OF THE BODIES,
AND THE EVIDENCE IS CONCLUSIVE.
THIS WAS A PROFESSIONAL JOB.
MOST LIKELY DONE BY--
- YEAH, IT WAS KASPER.
HIS SQUAD WAS BEHIND IT.
I'M SORRY
TO INTERRUPT YOUR REPORT.
- COLONEL?
- Man: WHAT DID YOU FIND, SIR?
- WHILE I WAS DRIVING,
I HEARD A CLEAR
ADMISSION OF GUILT.
NOT FROM THE HORSE'S MOUTH
EXACTLY, BUT CLOSE ENOUGH.
- Man: MY GOD.
- Kurosaka: WHAT NOW, SIR?
- BASTARD'S GUNNING FOR US.
- PLEASE, WE'RE IN CONTROL.
IN RESPONSE,
I'VE INITIALIZED PLAN K,
BUT WE'RE GONNA NEED
TO ALTER THE PLAN SIGNIFICANTLY.
OUR TARGET'S YOUNGER SISTER,
KOKO HEKMATYAR,
IS IN JAPAN WITH HER TEAM.
WE'LL CALL THIS OPERATION
DOUBLE K,
AND WE'RE MOVING
BEYOND COVERT OPS.
KOKO EMPLOYS HIGHLY
TRAINED MERCS
IN WAR ZONES ACROSS THE GLOBE.
THEY'RE EXPECTING US,
AND THEY KNOW HOW I THINK.
SO WE CONFUSE THEM.
OUR DAYS
AS THE FORGOTTEN UNIT ARE OVER.
WE'LL LAUNCH
A MULTI-PRONGED ATTACK,
FULL COMBAT SITUATIONS.
IT WILL GET MESSY.
- Both: YES, SIR.
WE HOPE IT DOES, SIR!
- I THOUGHT AS MUCH.
THANK YOU ALL
FOR BEING ON BOARD.
NOW LET'S CUT LOOSE.
- D.I.H.,
S.R. UNIT,
INVISIBLE GHOSTS AN' STUFF.
- KOKO,
IF YOU WANT TO GO TO SLEEP,
IT MIGHT BE EASIER
IF YOU CLIMB INTO BED FIRST.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DRINK
TO RELAX.
- WHAT?
JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE TALL,
YOU CAN'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
I CAN DRINK.
ACTUALLY I THINK
I'M GOOD AT IT.
AND BESIDES, WINE
TASTES, LIKE, AWESOME.
- OKAY, YOU'RE CUT OFF.
I KNOW YOU'RE A BADASS,
BUT YOU'VE STILL GOTTA
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
LET'S GET YOU A SHOWER.
WHAT?
WE SHOULD SHOWER TOGETHER?
IF YOU WANT TO.
I MEAN YOU'RE THE BOSS.
WHAT?!
WE SHOULD SHARE A BED
AFTERWARDS?
WELL, IT WOULD BE WARMER
THAT WAY.
AND A MASSAGE?!
SURE, I KNOW
ALL THE RIGHT TECHNIQUES.
YOU ARE IN GOOD HANDS, KOKO!
AND OTHER PARTS.
- IT'S CRAZY, JONAH.
THIS TRIP TO JAPAN
HAS ME FEELING NERVOUS
ONLY CARRYING A HANDGUN.
IT'S NOT SO EASY
TO PATROL AGAINST GHOSTS.
- LEHM SAID THIS COUNTRY'S SAFE.
I THINK PACKING HANDGUNS
IS ALL THE CRAZY
WE'RE GONNA NEED.
IF YOU ASK ME, KOKO'S THE
CRAZIEST PART OF THIS SITUATION,
MAKING SO MANY ENEMIES WE HAVE
TO BE ARMED TO THE TEETH
ALL THE TIME.
- IT DOES MAKE
FOR AN INTERESTING LIFE.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE WORKING
IN HELL,
YOU'RE BOUND
TO MEET A FEW DEVILS.
- WELL, KASPER MAY BE AN ASS,
BUT HE WOULDN'T BRING
HIS OWN SISTER HERE
IF HE DIDN'T THINK
WE WERE SAFE
WITH THE RESOURCES
AT OUR DISPOSAL.
HE KEPT HIS PROMISE,
SO I TRUST HIM.
- ( thinking ) IT'S FUNNY.
WHEN HE'S TALKING ABOUT KASPER,
SUDDENLY THE KID'S
A MOTOR-MOUTH.
- PLUS YOU SAID
THESE GUYS WORK IN THE SHADOWS,
SO THERE'S ZERO CHANCE
OF A SHOOTOUT.
- WELL YEAH, THOUGH I WOULDN'T
PUT ANYTHING AT ZERO.
- SEE? SO I CAN RELAX.
I WON'T EVEN HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT THOSE KIDS.
- UH-HUH.
( thinking ) HE'S THINKING
MORE ABOUT THOSE KIDS
THAN HE LETS ON.
BUT MORE SHOCKINGLY,
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I MADE A BUSINESS DEAL
WITH KASPER.
- ( phone vibrating )
- YES?
RIGHT, I UNDERSTAND.
I'LL TELL HER FIRST THING.
- WE'RE GONNA LOOK
LIKE A GROUP OF BACKPACKERS,
JUST WITH A FEW
TOO MANY BATTLE SCARS.
- ( Koko laughing )
YEAH, AND ARMED TO THE TEETH.
- SORRY, KID.
OBVIOUSLY YOU'RE DISAPPOINTED
IN ME.
- JONAH, TOJO WASN'T RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS ONE.
I'M THE ONE WHO MADE
THE DECISION
TO BRING THE HEAVY GUNS.
BUT I PROMISE YOU, A SHOOTOUT
IS THE LAST THING I WANT.
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT JAPAN
BEING SAFE,
AND THERE'S PROBABLY NO NEED
FOR US TO WORRY.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH HAVING A LITTLE FIREPOWER
JUST IN CASE.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE I SELL
THIS STUFF OR ANYTHING, RIGHT?
( chuckles )
NOW ABOUT TODAY,
SEEMS THE ILLUSTRIOUS S.R. UNIT
WANTS A MEET-UP.
COLONEL HINOKI
CALLED TOJO LATE LAST NIGHT
AND EMAILED ME TO CONFIRM.
HE WANTS TO PARLAY.
THE LOCATION IS THE PARKING AREA
AT UMIHOTARU.
WE'RE MEETING
UNDER THE PRETEXT
OF DIVIDING UP THE TRADING
TERRITORY IN SOUTHEAST ASIA.
LIKE THAT'LL HAPPEN.
THE S.R. MADE IT CLEAR
TALKING WOULDN'T RESOLVE THIS
WHEN THEY PULLED
THE FIRST TRIGGER.
SO WHAT'S THE POINT?
AND WHY NOW?
WHY LEAVE THE SHADOWS
INSTEAD OF MANEUVERING
COVERTLY TO KILL MY BROTHER,
LIKE TOJO ANTICIPATED?
USING A MEETING TO GET CLOSE
IS A COMMON TACTIC,
BUT NOT FOR THEM.
OUR OPPONENTS
HAVE BECOME ERRATIC,
AND INCREASINGLY
HARD TO READ.
HOW ARE WE TO REACT WHEN A GHOST
STOPS BEHAVING LIKE A GHOST?
AND WHAT'S THE S.R. UNIT
REALLY HOPING TO ACHIEVE?
WELL, THERE'S NO POINT
IN BROODING.
THIS IS BAIT WE HAVE TO TAKE.
THEY DON'T HAVE A BASE HERE,
SO WHEN THEY NEED
TO HOLD MEETINGS,
THEY USE RANDOM SERVICE AREAS
OFF THE HIGHWAY.
IF WE MISS THIS CHANCE, FINDING
THEM AGAIN WON'T BE EASY.
LET'S MOVE OUT.
- All: 'KAY.
- SO HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
TO UMIHOTARU BEFORE?
- NO. THEY DIDN'T
FINISH BUILDING IT UNTIL '97,
AND I'D ALREADY LEFT JAPAN
BY THEN.
- MMM.
- ( thinking ) HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT SHE'S RIGHT.
HINOKI'S METHODS HAVE CHANGED.
BUT WHY?
- OPERATION IS A GO.
- ( elevator dings )
- ( knocking )
- YOU HAVE A PROPOSAL
TO SPLIT THE SOUTHEAST ASIAN
ROUTE, MISS KUROSAKA?
- YES, I DO.
IT'S ONLY A PRELIMINARY DRAFT,
AS I'M SURE
YOU'LL WANNA WEIGH IN.
AND LET ME APOLOGIZE
ON BEHALF OF GANVILLE TRADING
FOR NOT SENDING A MORE
WORTHY REPRESENTATIVE
IN THIS FIRST MEETING.
IF WE'RE ABLE
TO REACH A COMPROMISE TODAY,
OUR EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR,
MISTER HINOKI,
WILL MAKE ARRANGEMENTS
TO MEET WITH YOU IN PERSON
TO HAMMER OUT
THE FINAL DETAILS.
AS YOU KNOW, WE ALSO FUNCTION
AS AN INTELLIGENCE AGENCY,
AND SO MUST TAKE PRECAUTIONS.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND,
OUR RUDENESS IS
NECESSARY FOR OUR SAFETY.
- IT'S FINE.
I REALLY DON'T CARE.
CAN I SEE THIS PROPOSAL?
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR
UNDERSTANDING, MR. KASPER.
THAT'S VERY GOOD OF YOU.
IN THAT CASE, WE'LL MOVE
RIGHT TO THE DOCUMENTS,
AS YOU'VE REQUESTED.
LET ME JUST FISH THEM OUT.
- WAKE UP, SIR. YOU SPACED OUT.
SHE'S AN ASSASSIN.
THE S.R. UNIT'S
MOVING AGAINST US.
- YEAH, I NOTICED.
NEARLY HAD
A GODDAMN HEART ATTACK.
MAN, SHE WAS FAST.
- NOT FAST ENOUGH, I GUESS.
SHE HAD THAT IN HER BELT, POE.
YOU MISSED IT.
- IT'S AN ULTRA-THIN KATANA.
THAT'S SO AWESOME.
- YET IT WAS STRONG ENOUGH
TO CARVE THROUGH MY BOOT
ALL THE WAY
TO THE STEEL SOLE GUARD.
I THINK I LIKE THESE GUYS.
- Kasper: THEY STILL COMING?
- Alan: UNKNOWN.
- HOW MANY?
- Poe: UNKNOWN.
- ORDERS, SIR?
- WE CAN'T SECURE THIS HOTEL.
WE'RE PULLING OUT.
KILL ON SIGHT.
I WANNA SEND A MESSAGE
TO THESE BASTARDS.
WE'LL HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THE LOCAL POLICE.
MAN, WHAT A PAIN.
( laughing )
TOJO?
YOU WERE WAY OFF THE MARK
ON THIS ONE.
WELL, I WON'T HOLD IT
AGAINST HIM.
HONESTLY, I WAS CAUGHT
WITH MY PANTS DOWN TOO.
DOESN'T MAKE SENSE--
THIS PLAY.
THEY SHOULD KNOW WE CAN DEFEND
AGAINST CRUDE ASSAULTS.
IS THE S.R.
UNDERESTIMATING US?
- Man: WE'VE LOST CONTACT.
KUROSAKA IS DEAD.
- WEDGE 'EM BETWEEN
THE NORTH AND SOUTH STAIRWELLS.
TEAM TWO, WHAT'S YOUR STATUS?
- ALL SET.
- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO ♪
♪ TIME TIME,
TIME TIME TO ATTACK... ♪
( song continues )
- ( gunfire continues )
- PLAYING SOLDIER'S TOUGH WORK,
ISN'T IT?
AND MY SOLDIERS ARE BETTER.
'CAUSE THEY'VE GOT
WAY MORE EXPERIENCE.
- YOU'RE HAPPY.
NOT THE MOOD I'D EXPECT
FROM A GUY UNDER ATTACK,
BOSS-MAN.
- I AM HAPPY. I'VE ALWAYS DREAMT
OF FIGHTING THESE GUYS,
OR THE GUYS BEFORE THEM,
TO BE MORE PRECISE.
AFTER VIETNAM, THE S.R. BUILT
ONE HELL OF A REP HERE,
FOR THOSE IN THE KNOW.
AND THEY BUILT IT WITH GRIT.
IT'S SAID THE JAPANESE
RAN THE ARMS TRADE
WITH PISTOLS
TUCKED IN THEIR PANTS.
THESE ARE THE CHILDREN OF MEN
WHO MADE AN EMPIRE
FROM THE UNDERWORLD.
AND I'VE BEEN TOLD
THEY BETRAYED MY FATHER.
OF COURSE I WANT TO FACE THEM.
BUT THIS IS NO STRIKE,
HE'S JUST TESTING ME.
COLONEL HINOKI NEEDS
TO STOP PLAYING
AND BRING ME A REAL FIGHT.
- I'LL BE DAMNED.
HOW'D YOU TURN OUT
LIKE THIS, KASPER?
AND YOU USED TO BE SO CUTE
WHEN YOU WERE YOUNGER.
- OH, NO,
LOOKS LIKE REINFORCEMENTS.
WHATEVER.
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU KILL 'EM ALL.
- ♪ TIME TIME TIME TIME
TO ATTACK. ♪
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪