- Koko: PROFESSOR MINAMI AMADA,
A.K.A. DR. MIAMI.
SHE SPECIALIZES IN ROBOTICS,
AND THE STUFF SHE WORKS ON
PRETTY MUCH ALWAYS
GETS CONVERTED
FOR MILITARY USE.
- YOU ARE KOKO HEKMATYAR?
I AM GUOMING CHEN.
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
- OUR MISSION IS TO SECURE
THIS WOMAN, DR. MIAMI.
AND IF ANYBODY OUT HERE
TRIES TO GET IN OUR WAY, WELL,
WE ELIMINATE 'EM, BOYS.
- Karen: I DON'T CARE
ABOUT THE DAMN DOCTOR.
IT'S HEKMATYAR'S PEOPLE I WANT.
I'LL SLAUGHTER THEM ALL
AND AVENGE THE MEN
WHOSE LIVES KASPER STOLE.
- VALMET?
- WHA--
WHY THE HELL
DID SHE BREAK RANKS?
- Lehm: EVERYONE,
COVER VALMET!
- ( knives stabbing )
- A WOLF IS COMING.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- DELICIOUS!
THIS IS THE BEST EGG ROLL EVER.
- I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE ENJOYING IT.
THEY COMBINE SHRIMP
CAUGHT IN ST. FRANCIS
WITH THE FRESHEST VEGETABLES
TO MAKE THEIR EGG ROLLS
SUPERIOR.
- OOH! AND THIS SPRING ROLL--
CRISPY, BUT STILL CHEWY.
- WE'RE ONLY JUST BEGINNING.
IF YOU AREN'T CAREFUL,
YOU'LL FILL UP
ON APPETIZERS ALONE.
- UGO, WOULDN'T IT BE AWESOME
TO BRING THE WHOLE CREW HERE?
- HUH?
YES, CERTAINLY.
- PLEASE, FEEL FREE
TO HELP YOURSELF.
- UH, NO THANK YOU,
I'M NOT HUNGRY.
NOT FOR THIS CRAP.
- I WISH JONAH COULD TRY THIS.
I'D LOVE TO SEE HIS FACE.
HE'S MISSIN' OUT.
- SORRY, MS. HEKMATYAR DOES NOT
CARE FOR WINE THIS EVENING.
( thinking ) THE BOSS LADY
IS AN UGLY DRUNK.
- ABSTAINING FROM ALCOHOL?
HOW ADMIRABLE.
- ( Scarecrow laughs )
EH, HOW BORING!
FOOD AND BOOZE.
DON'T THEY HAVE ANYTHING
MORE INTERESTING
TO TALK ABOUT OVER DINNER?
SCHOKOLADE, COME ON.
WE NEED TO RECORD THEM
TALKING ABOUT SOMETHING JUICY.
- WHAT EXACTLY DO YOU WANT ME
TO DO ABOUT IT?
IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN CONTROL
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING.
- WELL,
WHAT DO WE HAVE SO FAR?
ONE USELESS PHOTO OF THEM
OUT IN THE HALLWAY.
AND THEN IT'S STRAIGHT
INTO THE V.I.P. ROOM.
YOU DIDN'T FIGURE THEY'D
BE GIVEN SPECIAL TREATMENT HERE?
WHY CAN'T THE HOME OFFICE
SEND ME A USEFUL ASSISTANT
AT LEAST ONCE IN A WHILE?
THIS TIME I'M STUCK
WITH A GLUTTONOUS BIMBO.
- I AM NOT A BIMBO,
THANK YOU.
IT TOOK SKILL FOR ME TO GET IN
THAT ROOM, LET ALONE BUG IT.
SO SHUT UP.  PERSONALLY,
I'M JUST SURPRISED
THAT WHAT I'VE HEARD ABOUT
YOU IS TRUE.
YOU ACTUALLY ARE
AS BIG OF A DICK
AS EVERYONE SAID YOU WOULD BE.
WHAT, NOT GONNA EAT?
I TOTALLY AGREE WITH KOKO.
THE FOOD HERE IS AWESOME.
- ( thinking )
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
HOW LONG ARE THEY GONNA
KEEP THIS FARCE UP?
DAMN IT.
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
LET ME INTRODUCE MYSELF.
MAJOR SOPHIA VELMER,
OR, RATHER, EX-MAJOR.
YOUR FIGHTING TECHNIQUE
IS QUITE UNUSUAL.
I WOULD REALLY LOVE
TO HEAR MORE ABOUT IT.
- I'M NOT MUCH FOR TALKING.
- OH, DON'T WORRY.
I WOULD BE MORE THAN HAPPY
TO TALK TO YOUR DEAD BODY.
I'M SURE IT WOULD BE
A GREAT CONVERSATION.
- ( gunfire continues )
- HMM.
I CAN'T SLEEP LIKE THIS.
I MEAN,
WHAT'S WITH THE FIREWORKS?
- THE FOOD WILL BE READY SOON.
A HOT MEAL SHOULD HELP YOU
FALL ASLEEP, OKAY?
- YEAH, I'M SURE IT WILL.
- THERE'S A BATTLE OUT THERE,
AND IT'S GETTING CLOSER.
BUT THE WAY IT'S ECHOING,
I CAN'T TELL WHERE IT IS.
- THEN AGAIN,
MAYBE THAT'S THE SOUND
OF KOKO HOT ON MY HEELS.
THE ECHO OF GUNFIRE FOLLOWS
WHEREVER THAT WOMAN WALKS.
- ( laughs )
- I AM TOTALLY NOT JOKING,
YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, NO MATTER
WHERE SHE GOES,
SHE ALWAYS MANAGES TO GET
INTO A FIGHT WITH SOMEBODY.
- THAT PROBABLY HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH
THE LINE OF WORK SHE'S IN.
- YEAH YEAH.
FUNNY THING IS,
SHE INSISTS THAT SHE DOESN'T
SEEK OUT VIOLENCE.
I CAN'T COUNT HOW MANY
TIMES SHE'S SAID THAT.
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
NOTHING GOOD EVER COMES
FROM THE WEAPONS TRADE.
WHETHER YOU'RE IN IT
BY CHOICE OR BY FORCE,
YOU'RE SCREWED.
YOU'RE A TOOTH,
CAUGHT BETWEEN TWO COGS.
THERE'S NO CHANGING IT.
SURE, I COULD TRY
TO BE STUBBORN
AND INSIST THAT
I'LL DESIGN ROBOTS
ONLY FOR
CHILDREN'S ENTERTAINMENT.
IT WOULDN'T HELP.
THE COGS WOULD CRUSH ME
INTO SAND AND KEEP ON TURNING.
YOU KNOW WHEN I FIRST REALIZED
THAT WAS HOW THINGS WERE?
I'D DEVELOPED AN ADORABLE
ROBOTIC STUFFED ANIMAL
FOR THREE YEAR OLDS.
AND THEY TURNED IT
INTO A MISSILE WARHEAD.
- THAT IS A SHITTY SITUATION.
WHY DO YOU STILL
ASSOCIATE WITH H.C.L.I.
AND THE DA XINGHAI COMPANY?
SURELY YOU COULD CUT
THOSE TIES, AT LEAST?
- PARTIALLY IT'S BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO STOP MYSELF.
I GUESS I LIKE THE PERKS
OF SPENDING TIME
WITH A WEALTHY MAN
LIKE MR. CHEN.
AS FOR KOKO,
I SEE SOMETHING IN HER THA--
THE FOOD!
THE NOODLES ARE OVERCOOKED.
- OH, JEEZ!
SORRY, DOC.
OW, HOT!
- AW, MAN!
MOKO, I DON'T LIKE THEM
UNLESS THEY'RE AL DENTE.
- Chen: MS. HEKMATYAR?
ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
- SAY WHAT?
OH, YES, THANK YOU.
ANOTHER EXCELLENT WINE.
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
I'M GLAD I SELECTED SOMETHING
TO YOUR LIKING.
- ( thinking ) SHE SHOULD REALLY
BE CUT OFF ABOUT NOW.
- I WOULD LOVE TO SHARE A BOTTLE
WITH YOUR ELDER BROTHER
AS WELL SOMETIME.
- ( laughs )
I DON'T THINK THAT WOULD
BE NEARLY AS ENJOYABLE.
MY BROTHER GULPS HIS BEVERAGES
RATHER THAN SAVORING THEM.
HE PREFERS JUNK FOOD
TO FINE DINING.
NOT THAT I DON'T CRAVE
THE OCCASIONAL BURGER.
- I'VE NOT HAD THE
PLEASURE OF MEETING
MR. HEKMATYAR IN PERSON,
BUT SOME OF MY ASSOCIATES
IN CENTRAL ASIA
HAVE HAD THE OPPORTUNITY.
- THERE, MUCH BETTER.
NOW THEY GOT SOME DRINKS IN 'EM,
THEY'RE FINALLY
STARTING TO TALK.
- ISN'T THIS A LITTLE
TOO CONVENIENT?
EARTH TO SCARECROW.
- HUH?
- CHEN'S POSING
AS A LEGITIMATE BUSINESSMAN,
BUT HE BASICALLY JUST ADMITTED
TO INVOLVEMENT WITH
THE ARMS TRADE.
AND IT KINDA SEEMED
LIKE HE WAS HINTING
THAT HE'S GOT TROOPS
OF HIS OWN TOO.
- THAT'S THE REASON WE BUGGED
HIM IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THIS IS JUST THE
KIND OF INFORMATION
WE WERE HOPING TO HEAR,
SO TRY NOT TO
FREAK OUT ON ME NOW.
STILL, THERE'S A LOT MORE
I WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT HOW THIS GUY WORKS.
HE'S FRONTING AN HONEST BUSINESS
AND DEALING WEAPONS.
AND I'M GOING TO KEEP ON HIM
UNTIL I KNOW HOW.
- Chen:
FROM WHAT I HAVE GATHERED,
YOU AND YOUR BROTHER
OPERATE IN VERY DIFFERENT WAYS.
I FIRST CAME TO THAT REALIZATION
WHEN I LEARNED THAT,
LIKE ME,
YOU'VE HAD REPEATED CONTACT
WITH ONE DR. MINAMI AMADA.
IF I MAY BE SO BOLD,
WHAT IS ON THE HORIZON FOR
YOUR BUSINESS, MS. HEKMATYAR?
- THAT'S A SECRET.
- I CAN'T HELP
BUT THINK YOU AND I
ARE AFTER EXACTLY
THE SAME THING.
IT IS MY HOPE THAT WE CAN
WORK TOGETHER TOWARD THAT GOAL.
- I'LL HAVE TO DECLINE.
- IF SOMEONE HAS TIED
YOUR HANDS IN THIS,
PERHAPS I CAN HELP YOU
BREAK FREE.
- ( gunfire continues )
- I THOUGHT SO.
THE WAY YOU MOVE
IS NEARLY IDENTICAL
TO THE MAN
WHO ANNIHILATED MY UNIT.
ALL THESE YEARS
COMING UP EMPTY HANDED,
AND NOW A CLUE DROPS
INTO MY LAP.
AS YOU CAN GUESS,
I'M QUITE EXCITED.
- LIKE I GIVE A DAMN.
- ( gun cocks )
- R: AWESOME.
I KNEW SHE WAS GOOD,
BUT DAMN.
I COULDN'T FIGHT LIKE THAT
IN A MILLION YEARS.
- ( gunfire )
- ( Lutz grunts )
- I GOT HIT,
SHOT RIGHT IN THE ASS.
- WOW, LUTZ,
THAT'S PRETTY PATHETIC.
SERVES YOU RIGHT, THOUGH,
FOR LETTING YOUR GUARD DOWN.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY JUST A SCRATCH,
SO STOP CRYING.
GET IT TOGETHER, MAN.
WE STILL GOT WORK TO DO.
- Jonah: LEHM,
THEY'RE MOVING.
I THINK ALL THE RANDOM GUNFIRE'S
STARTING TO GET TO THEM.
- SOUNDS LIKE SHELL-SHOCK.
COMBAT FATIGUE
IS WEARING THEM DOWN,
SO THEY'RE
BREAKING COVER, RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
APART FROM THE LIEUTENANT,
NONE OF THEM KNOW HOW TO FIGHT
IN THE MOUNTAINS.
THEY'VE PROBABLY ALWAYS BEEN
STATIONED IN CITIES.
I SAY WE JUST PUT DOWN
OUR WEAPONS AND PLAY DEAD.
THEY'LL ALL STAND UP,
THINKING THEY'RE SAFE.
AND THEN YOU CAN START
PICKING 'EM OFF, ONE BY ONE.
- ( laughs )
- THE SHOOTING'S STOPPED.
- ( panting )
- ( gunshot )
- ONE MOMENT OF WEAKNESS
AND YOU'RE DEAD.
BUT THAT'S COMBAT FOR YOU--
CRUEL AND UGLY.
- THIS REALLY SUCKS.
I GET ALL THE CRAPPY JOBS.
- HEKMATYAR'S IN THE BATHROOM.
SHE MIGHT USE THIS CHANCE
TO CALL HER PEOPLE.
GET IN THERE
AND CHECK IT OUT.
- EH, I'M ALREADY HERE,
I MIGHT AS WELL.
- ( toilet flushes )
- ( door rattling )
- AHH! HEY!  WHA--
HEY, DO YOU MIND?
SOMEONE'S IN HERE!
- SCHOKOLADE, HUH?
- KOKO?  WAIT A MINUTE!
YOU USED MY CODENAME.
HOW DO YOU EVEN
HAVE THAT INFORMATION?
- BECAUSE I MADE IT
A SPECIAL POINT
TO CHECK INTO ALL OF SCARECROW'S
KNOWN ASSOCIATES.
- AH!  WHAT THE HELL?
CAN'T I GET SOME PRIVACY?
- IN A SEC.
ONE THING FIRST.
I HAVE A MESSAGE
YOU SHOULD PASS ON TO YOUR BOSS
IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO END UP DEAD.
- LIEUTENANT!
- ( gunshot )
- AHHH!
- SHE DODGED THEM ALL!
- YOU DON'T NEED THIS ARM.
- AHHH!
AHH!
- YOU MAKE A LOT OF NOISE.
IF YOU'VE GOT
THE STRENGTH TO SCREAM,
YOU'VE GOT THE STRENGTH TO TALK.
YOU CAN START
BY TELLING ME YOUR NAME.
SHOULD BE SIMPLE ENOUGH.
COME ON, YOU CAN SPEAK,
CAN'T YOU?
I HAVEN'T SLIT YOUR THROAT YET.
YOU'RE WEAK. CAN YOU HEAR ME?
YOU'RE WEAK!
( thinking )
AND ME?  AM I SO STRONG?
MY UNIT.
BECAUSE I COULDN'T CUT IT
AS COMMANDING OFFICER.
THEY'RE ALL--
- IT'S TIME TO PULL OUT,
VALMET.  LET'S GO.
WE STILL GOT A MISSION
TO COMPLETE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT HER.
I'VE TAKEN OUT HER ENTIRE UNIT,
THANKS TO SOME QUICK THINKING
ON JONAH'S PART.
- NO, HOLD ON.
SHE KNOWS SOMETHING
ABOUT MY PAST.
- SO WHAT THEN?
YOU WANNA TAKE HER WITH YOU
AND TORTURE HER TILL SHE TALKS?
THAT'S NOT HOW WE OPERATE.
- WHAT A WASTE OF TIME.
RIGHT NOW YOU'RE
IN THE SAME PLACE I ONCE WAS.
CHEW ON THAT FOR A WHILE.
- MAJOR VELMER.
KAREN LOW, LIEUTENANT
IN THE PEOPLE'S LIBERATION ARMY.
DON'T FORGET.
IT'S THE NAME OF THE WOMAN
WHO WILL KILL YOU.
- SEE YOU AROUND THEN,
KAREN.
- Lehm: THAT TOOK FOREVER.
IT'S PRACTICALLY DAWN ALREADY.
- YOU BIMBO.
WHAT DUMBASS IDEAS DID HEKMATYAR
PUT IN YOUR EMPTY LITTLE HEAD?
MY JOB IS TO SEE
THAT JUSTICE IS DONE
BY TAKING THE MONEY THOSE CROOKS
WORK SO VERY HARD TO EARN.
THAT'S HOW THIS GOES.
I'M NOT ABOUT TO TURN AROUND
AND GIVE IT BACK TO THEM.
LISTEN, HON,
I'M WELL AWARE THAT CHEN
IS A DANGEROUS MAN.
I DON'T NEED ANYONE
TO TELL ME THAT.
I GOT THINGS UNDER CONTROL.
YOU AND ME ARE GONNA
LEAVE CHINATOWN IN ONE PIECE.
YOU KNOW, THAT MAN HAS PROBABLY
KILLED TENS OF THOUSANDS
OF PEOPLE IN HIS TIME.
BUT WHEN YOU'RE A PRO LIKE ME,
YOU CAN TELL THESE THINGS
JUST FROM A MAN'S FACE.
- WONDERFUL.  SO THIS GUY
IS BASICALLY A KILLING MACHINE.
WOULDN'T IT BE SAFER
TO THROW IN OUR LOT WITH KOKO?
- HUH?
- THINK ABOUT IT.
IF CHEN KILLS HEKMATYAR,
YOU WON'T GET A CENT OUT OF HER.
WE'RE OUT OF TIME HERE.
- ( cell phone ringing )
- SORRY, DO YOU MIND?
THIS MIGHT BE
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
KOKO HERE.
A-CHEW!
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME,
I'M NOT FEELING SO WELL.
I THINK IT WOULD BE BEST
IF WE CALLED IT A NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR A LOVELY DINNER.
- IT WAS MY PLEASURE.
I'M JUST GRATEFUL
YOU COULD FIND THE TIME
TO MEET WITH ME THIS EVENING.
I HOPE YOU'LL UNDERSTAND
IF I DON'T WALK YOU OUT.
- OF COURSE, MR. CHEN,
I'LL FIND MY OWN WAY.
THE MEAL WAS EXCELLENT.
YOU TAKE CARE NOW.
- Man: TARGETS?
- Li: FOUR, TOTAL.
TAKE OUT HEKMATYAR AND HER MAN
AND THE AMERICANS
THAT ARE WITH THEM.
TRY TO MAKE IT LOOK LIKE THEY
WERE MUGGED OR SOMETHING.
- ROGER.
- AHHH!
- GENERAL!
- FROM THE SOUND OF THINGS,
MR. CHEN COULDN'T QUITE
HIDE HIS TRUE FEELINGS
UNTIL WE WERE GONE.
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- DON'T WORRY.
LEHM AND THE OTHERS
CAME OUT ON TOP.
- KOKO, OVER HERE!
- MOVE YOUR LILY-WHITE ASS.
- SEE THAT?
I'VE ARRANGED FOR OUR
SAFE PASSAGE AWAY FROM HERE.
SUH-WEEET!
THE SUPER HIND M.K.5
IS ALREADY OPERATIONAL?
- Scarecrow: IT'S A PROTOTYPE.
NOW GET THE FUCK ONBOARD.
- THEY GOT AWAY
IN A HELICOPTER.
- DAMN YOU, KOKO HEKMATYAR!
DAMN YOU, H.C.L.I.!
- PRETTY INCREDIBLE.
THIS IS THE ONLY SPOT
ON THE MOUNTAIN THAT'S WARM,
AND IT'S FILLED
WITH BUTTERFLIES.
- WA-HOO!
HMM.
SIMILAR IN APPEARANCE,
BUT NOT QUITE IT.
THAT SPECIES IS ACTUALLY HOSTILE
TO THE ONE I'M LOOKING FOR.
AND THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM.
THERE'S NO WAY PROFESSOR JAMES
WOULD MAKE A MISTAKE LIKE THIS.
DID SOMEONE SEND ME
FALSE INFORMATION?
- THEY ARE PRETTY, THOUGH.
- TRUE.
AND THIS VALLEY ITSELF
IS QUITE A FIND.
THERE MAY BE NEW SPECIES.
HI-YA!
AHHHH!
- I FOUND THE DOCTOR.
- Miami: A KID WITH A GUN.
ARE YOU KOKO'S MEN?
- I WANT THE WHOLE AREA
CLEARED.
- HAVEN'T SEEN YOU
WITH THE TEAM BEFORE.
SO, HON,
DO YOU HAVE A NAME?
- Koko: ARGH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SHE DITCHED ME TWICE IN A ROW!
- DAMN YOU, MINAMI!
- I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY!
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO VERY SORRY!
- AGAIN MALIN, NO NEED TO
APOLOGIZE. IT'S MY FAULT TOO.
I HAD A LITTLE TROUBLE
GETTING UP THIS MORNING.
- ( laughing )
- BUT I CAN JUST IMAGINE
YOUR STRUGGLE.
YOU DESPERATELY TRIED
TO STOP HER FROM LEAVING.
BUT SHE USED HER CLEVER WILES
TO SNEAK AWAY.
- YOU UNDERSTAND.
THANK YOU.
- SO WHICH BUTTERFLY THIS TIME?
- OH, SHE SAID
IT WAS SOME KIND OF SHELLFISH.
- SHELLFISH?
I WAS DITCHED FOR SHELLFISH?
THIS IS A NEW LOW.
OH, WELL, AT LEAST SHE GOT
THE BASIC THEORY COMPLETED.
BUT I WILL SO KICK HER ASS
IF SHE BLOWS ME OFF
AGAIN IN SIX MONTHS.
- I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY...
- SERIOUSLY, MALIN,
STOP IT WITH THE APOLOGIZING.
TO THE BAT CAVE!
- YES MA'AM.
- HONESTLY, WHY DOES NOTHING
EVER SEEM TO GO RIGHT
WHEN WE'RE IN AFRICA?
- YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT,
KOKO.
I KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- I BET YOU DO.
- THE LAND IS HARSH AND VAST.
AND TOO MANY OF ITS PEOPLE
LIVE IN CHAOS.
EVERYTHING HERE
SEEMS JUST OUT OF REACH.
DAMN IT, LEHM!
FOR THE MILLIONTH TIME,
NO SMOKING IN THE CAR.
- YEAH YEAH.
SORRY.  JEEZ.
- Koko: NEXT STOP, ENGLAND.
- LOOK AT THIS.
THERE ARE A TON OF THEM, MOKO.
- YES, DOCTOR.
- Koko:
MAN, IT'S CROWDED IN HERE.
NOT THAT I MIND.
IT MAKES
FOR GOOD PEOPLE WATCHING.
THAT WAS ROUGH.
- SORRY.
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
ARE YOU OKAY?
- I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST THAT WE NEEDED
TO GET AWAY FROM THAT RESTAURANT
SO QUICKLY, WE HAD TO LEAVE
BEHIND THE CREW'S NICE NEW CAR.
FULL-ON BULLET-PROOF WINDOWS,
ARMORED BODY.
THAT WAS A COSTLY LOSS.
- ( Mao laughs )
I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN.
BUT AT LEAST HUMAN CASUALTIES
WERE REMARKABLY LOW.
NONE DEAD AND ONLY TWO INJURED.
THINK OF IT THIS WAY--
THE CAR DIED
INSTEAD OF ONE OF US.
- HUH.
I KINDA LIKE THAT.
WHAT A GREAT WAY
OF LOOKING AT IT, MAO.
I HAVE AN IDEA--
WHY DON'T YOU GO OVER THERE
AND EXPLAIN
YOUR PERSPECTIVE TO UGO.
HE'S BEEN IN MOURNING
EVER SINCE IT HAPPENED.
HE WAS REALLY ATTACHED
TO THAT CAR.
- AW, JEEZ, I DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S NOT GONNA BE
AN EASY TASK.
- Woman over P.A.:
BANGKOK, HONG KONG, BALI,
AND SYDNEY, FLIGHT 806,
NOW BOARDING FROM GATE FIVE.
- Koko: WELL, SHOOT.
IT WAS WORTH A TRY ANYWAY.
- ( alarm sounding )
- HOLD ON, KID.
YOU'RE NOT CARRYING
ANY METAL OBJECTS, ARE YOU?
SORRY, SON, BUT WE CAN'T
LET YOU THROUGH SECURITY
UNTIL WE FIND OUT WHAT'S
MAKING YOU BEEP LIKE THAT.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S BEEPING 'CAUSE I GOT
A BULLET IN MY BUTT CHEEK.
- COME ON, YOU HEARD THE KID.
JONAH HERE HAS GOT A BULLET
IN HIS BUTT, THAT'S ALL.
- YES, THAT'S CORRECT,
OFFICER!
I KNOW--
STRANGE BUT TRUE.
THE POOR LITTLE THING
HAS A BULLET IN HIS REAR
FROM AN OLD INJURY.
- OH, I SEE.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE JUST JOKING.
VERY WELL, THEN.
- HE'S LETTING YOU THROUGH.
AND HE ONLY HAD TO BE
TOLD THREE TIMES.
THAT'S SECURITY FOR YOU.
- HEY, IF THERE'S A KID
HOLDING UP THE LINE,
IT'S HIS DAMN
PARENTS' FAULT. HONESTLY!
- THERE A PROBLEM BACK THERE?
- I'M SO SORRY.
- ( grunts )
- I CANNOT BELIEVE
YOU JUST MADE MY BOSS
APOLOGIZE TO YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOU GET TO SKIP THE
LINE IF YOU'RE IN A WHEELCHAIR.
I WOULD BE HAPPY TO ARRANGE
THAT FOR YOU IF YOU'D LIKE.
- THAT'S ENOUGH, VALMET!
WE DON'T BEAT UP ON CIVILIANS.
COME ON, LEHM, WHY AREN'T YOU
DOING SOMETHING TO STOP HER?
- I DUNNO,
'CAUSE IT'S FUCKIN' FUNNY?
- Koko: SWEET JEEBUS!
CAN'T WE EVEN CHANGE PLANES
WITHOUT MAKING A HUGE SCENE?
- SORRY, KOKO, I DIDN'T LIKE
HOW HE WAS TALKING TO YOU.
- ( laughs )
AW, THAT POOR SAP.
HE JUST WANTED TO ENJOY
HIS VACATION.
- I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
THERE WAS ALL THIS COMMOTION
OVER ONE LITTLE BULLET
IN JONAH'S ASS.
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
A BULLET IN THE ASS
IS A SERIOUS THING.
- ( laughs )
- WHY DON'T YOU GET IT REMOVED?
IT WOULD BE RELATIVELY
MINOR SURGERY,
NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.
- SURGERY DOESN'T SCARE ME.
IT'S JUST...
I DON'T LIKE NEEDLES.
- ( grunting )
- ( objects crashing )
- All: SCARED OF NEEDLES?
WHAT ARE YOU, A KID?
OH, YEAH.
YOU ARE A KID.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪