- ( woman singing opera )
- ( gunshot )
- ( screaming )
- DECENT VOICE, I GUESS,
BUT IT DIDN'T REALLY
DO ANYTHING FOR ME.
THE ONLY TRUE SOURCE OF MUSIC
IS ORCHESTRA.
AMEN.
WELL,
WE GOT A LIVE ONE, DO WE?
- ( whimpering )
- THAT SOUND'S MUSIC
TO MY EARS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( panting )
- I GOT A VISUAL.
GRAB 'EM NOW?
- NO, FLANK THEM.
WE'LL USE THE CAR AS A SHIELD.
- LOOKS LIKE WE GOT SOME LIVELY
NEW PLAYERS IN THE PIT.
- GUESS I'LL HAVE TO STEP ON IT.
- A NEGEV?
HE HAS A NEGEV LMG?
FINE.
LET'S DO THIS, ORCHESTRA.
- HIT THE TIRES.
- YEAH, NO SHIT.  I'M TRYING.
- KEEP RUNNING, BOSS LADY.
- HIT THE CODA ONCE MORE,
THEN I THINK IT'S TIME
WE WRAP THIS SHOW UP.
- TOTALLY.
- GOOD LORD.
DAMN IT.  KOKO, LISTEN UP.
THEY'VE GOT AN M-2
BROWNING MACHINE GUN
MOUNTED INSIDE THAT VEHICLE.
- WHAT?  ARE THEY CRAZY?
- Chinatsu: STILL WISH I DIDN'T
HAVE TO TAKE OUT THE CUTE BOY.
HIS FRIENDS
ARE JOINING HIM, THOUGH,
SO AT LEAST
HE'LL HAVE COMPANY.
- R, CONCENTRATE FIRE
ON THE ENGINE BLOCK.
THEY'LL DO THEIR BEST
TO FORCE YOU OUT OF THE WAY.
- ENSEMBLE.
- FIRE.
- BRACE FOR IMPACT.
- YEAH, NO SHIT.
- WHAT?!
- HURRY, IT MIGHT BLOW.
- SON OF A BITCH.
- ( gunfire )
- DAMN IT.
LITTLE SHIT IS STILL ALIVE.
AND THAT'S GOTTA MEAN
HIS LADY BOSS IS, TOO.
- GET BACK!
NO, MY HAT.
MAESTRO, WE GOTTA SCRUB
THE OPERATION.
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG.
LET'S PULL BACK
AND TRY AGAIN LATER.
- HUH?  RUN JUST BECAUSE
YOUR HAT GOT SHOT UP?
WASTING YOUR TIME
ON SUPERSTITION.
I SHOULD HAVE
THROWN IT AWAY.  UGH!
- MAESTRO!
SNIPER.
- HEART SHOT.  HIT.
TARGET WILL FALL TO HIS KNEES.
HEAD SHOT.  AIM.  FIRE.
HEAD SHOT.
HIT.
- ( screaming )
- THE GAP BETWEEN REPORT AND
IMPACT INDICATES A SHOT FIRED
FROM ROUGHLY 900 METERS AWAY.
MOST LIKELY USING
A .338 LAPUA MAGNUM.
IT WAS LUTZ'S SHOT.
NOW TO SEE IF CHINATSU
ENTERS HIS LINE OF SIGHT.
- NO.
NO, THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
YOU GAVE ME A NEW LIFE,
MAESTRO.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME NOW.
YOU CAN'T.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
- LUTZ, ORDER IS
TO PULL BACK.
- WHAT?
WE STILL HAVE ONE TARGET LEFT.
- YEAH, BUT THAT LITTLE GIRL
HAS THE REFLEXES OF A CAT.
BESIDES,
EVEN IF YOU GOT A BEAD ON HER,
WOULD YOU REALLY SHOOT?
- I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU.
HEAR ME?  I'LL KILL YOU ALL.
- WAIT, A HIT MAN
WANTS ME DEAD?
- NOT NOW.  IN A FEW DAYS
OR MAYBE A FEW MONTHS.
NO, BETTER IF I TAKE MY TIME.
- SHE IS LOSING IT.
- I'LL HUNT YOU DOWN AND RIP YOU
APART PIECE BY PIECE!
- HE HAS THE SHOT NOW.
- Lutz: A GIRL?
SHE'S JUST A KID.
- WE CAN'T ELIMINATE TARGET TWO,
BUT WE CAN DESTROY HER WEAPONS.
DO IT, LUTZ.
- OH.
- SHE'S QUICK.  DAMN!
- ( horn honks )
- GOODBYE, MAESTRO.
- WHAT THE HELL?
THAT GIRL,
SHE WASN'T WEARING PANTIES.
- ( siren wailing )
- HEY, THERE.
DON'T WASTE TIME
PUTTING UP A FIGHT.
KOKO HEKMATYAR, LOOKS LIKE WE
CAUGHT YOU RED-HANDED THIS TIME.
- CAUGHT ME DOING WHAT?
- PLAYING DUMB
WON'T DO ANY GOOD.
I PERSONALLY WITNESSED
THE ENTIRE GUNFIGHT.
- YOU MAY HAVE A POLICE OFFICER
WITH YOU, BUT YOU'RE NO COP.
WHO ARE YOU?
- OH, NOBODY SPECIAL.
I'M JUST A CITIZEN.
YOU'VE HEARD OF
A CITIZEN'S ARREST, I ASSUME.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
- ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'S THE PLAY, KOKO?
- NO PLAY.  SHE'S COMING
WITH ME, YOU LITTLE SHIT.
HOPE YOU ENJOY YOUR SWIM.
TAKE CARE.
TELL YOUR GUARDS TO STAND DOWN
AND WE'LL--
- HUH?  WHAT WAS THAT?
YOUR SIGNAL
FOR STRATEGIC RETREAT?
LEARN SOMETHING EVERY DAY.
WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING
IN INTERROGATION?
EXTREMELY POOR MANNERS, BRO.
I SO HELPED YOU GUYS OUT TODAY.
- YOU USED PHYSICAL FORCE
ON ONE OF MY OFFICERS
WHILE HE WAS ATTEMPTING
TO PERFORM HIS DUTIES.
WE FIND THAT KIND OF
BEHAVIOR UNACCEPTABLE,
AS WOULD MOST LAW ENFORCEMENT
AGENCIES, I'M SURE.
WE'LL LET YOU OFF WITH
A WARNING THIS TIME,
PROVIDED YOU CAN OFFER PROOF
THAT YOU REALLY ARE
AN INTELLIGENCE OFFICER.
AH, AMERICAN, I SEE.
- I SURE AM.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
- COULD YOU VERIFY YOUR NAME,
PLEASE?
- I'M JERRY SCHATZBERG.
HAH!  KIDDING.
MY HANDLE IS SCARECROW.
THAT'S HOW YOU CAN REFER
TO ME IN YOUR PAPERWORK, OKAY?
ACTUALLY, I DON'T GIVE A DAMN
ABOUT THE PAPERWORK.
IT'S THE ARMS DEALER
I'M INTERESTED IN.
HAND OVER KOKO HEKMATYAR
AND ANYTHING YOU'VE GOT ON HER,
ESPECIALLY FROM TODAY
LIKE FOOTAGE OF THE SHOOTOUT.
- WHAT SHOOTOUT?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
- WHAT?
- Koko: THANK YOU FOR THE SHOWER
AND CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER NOW.
- THAT MAKES ONE OF US.
- AW, YOU'RE NOT FEELING WELL?
I'M SORRY.  IS IT A COLD?
- NO, NOT A COLD.
MORE LIKE A HEADACHE.
YOU MADE QUITE A SCENE.
THAT LITTLE SKIRMISH ATTRACTED
SOME UNWANTED ATTENTION.
YOU KNOW CIA AGENT SCARECROW?
- YEAH, WE'VE MET.
HE'S IN A NON-COMBAT ZONE,
SO HE'S PROBABLY BROKE,
LOOKING FOR A NEW BACKER.
PERSISTENT, IS HE?
- OH, YEAH.
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE HIM?
- VERY MUCH SO.
- IT WILL BE HARD TO COVER
THIS UP AND EXPENSIVE.
WE LOST MEN, YOU KNOW?
SOME OFFICERS HAVE YOUR
BODYGUARDS IN CUSTODY.
THEY'RE BEING HELD
IN A LOCAL HOTEL.
A SLAP ON THE WRIST
TO HELP ME SAVE FACE.
HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND.
- NOW THAT JUST HURTS.
- GIVE MY REGARDS
TO YOUR FATHER.
- YOU'VE GOT ENOUGH
OF THE GUNFIGHT RECORDED
TO MAKE A WHOLE
FREAKIN' ACTION MOVIE.
THIS CITY IS COVERED
IN SECURITY CAMERAS.
- GET OFF THE DESK NOW
OR I WILL SHOOT YOU.
- CAN'T BELIEVE THIS BULLSHIT.
WHAT KIND OF SHENANIGANS
YOU TRYING TO PULL?
'CAUSE WHATEVER IT IS,
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK ON ME.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
WHO ARE YOU TEXTING?
NOW I GET IT.
- Officer: WE'RE NOT DONE HERE.
SIT BACK DOWN.
- GET THE HELL OFF OF ME.
- WAIT!  UGH!
- COME ON,
WHERE ARE YOU, BACK DOOR?
HEKMATYAR,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- OH, IT'S YOU.  HEY.
- PLAYING NICE NOW?
AND YOU'VE EVEN GOT THE BALLS TO
MARCH RIGHT OUT THE FRONT DOOR.
YOU MADE ME LOOK LIKE
AN IDIOT TODAY.
I DON'T APPRECIATE THAT.
- GRAB HIM!
TIGHTER!
- YEAH, I'M TRYING.
- ( Scarecrow laughing )
- I DON'T HAVE TIME TO WASTE
ON A GNAT LIKE YOU.
- SUCH ARROGANCE.
GO AHEAD, ENJOY YOUR MONEY
AND YOUR POWER WHILE YOU CAN.
PRISON WOULD BE TOO GOOD
FOR YOU ANYWAY.
YOU HEAR ME?
I'M GONNA HUNT YOU DOWN.
AND WHEN I FIND YOU, I'LL TEAR
YOU APART, LIMB FROM LIMB.
- GET IN LINE.
YOU'RE THE SECOND PERSON TODAY
WHO'S TOLD ME THAT.
- Chinatsu:
RIP YOU APART PIECE BY PIECE!
- Police chief: SOME OFFICERS
HAVE YOUR BODYGUARDS IN CUSTODY.
- Koko:
I'M A SITTING DUCK OUT HERE.
- ( gasps )
YOU!
- YEAH, ME.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR FACE?
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY PUNCHED YOU.
- THAT ASSHOLE FROM BEFORE.
NOTHING TO BE WORRIED ABOUT.
THE POLICE COMMANDER TOLD ME YOU
GUYS WERE BEING HELD
IN SOME HOTEL.
STILL WET, AWESOME.
- THEY DIDN'T KEEP ME.  I'M
YOUNG AND INNOCENT, YOU KNOW?
- PURE AS THE DRIVEN SNOW.
YEAH, THAT'S YOU.
WELL, SHALL WE GO?
GOOD.
ONWARD HO, OFFICER JONAH.
YOU'RE A NICE KID,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU CAME DOWN TO THE STATION
BECAUSE YOU WANTED
TO LOOK OUT FOR ME.
- NICE KIDS DON'T SHOOT PEOPLE
IN THE FACE.
- THAT'S NOT NECESSARILY TRUE.
- THESE DAYS, EVEN SAINTS
GO AROUND WITH WEAPONS,
PREACHING GOD'S LOVE
TO THE SOUND OF GUNFIRE.
IN THE END, IT'S ALL ABOUT
WHAT YOU BELIEVE IN,
WHAT MAKES YOU PULL
THAT TRIGGER.
IMAGINE SOMETHING FOR ME.
YOUR BULLETS ARE HARD SHELLS,
CONCEALING WITHIN THEM
THE KINDNESS OF YOUR SOUL.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES YOU UNLIKE
ANY OTHER SOLDIER I'VE MET.
IT BAFFLES ME.
HOW DO YOU HAVE
ANY KINDNESS LEFT
AFTER EVERYTHING YOU'VE ENDURED?
I MEAN, AFTER ALL, DON'T YOU
DESPISE ALL ARMS DEALERS?
- EXCEPT FOR YOU.
YOU'RE OKAY.
- OH, I'M THE ONLY ONE
YOU DON'T HATE, AM I?
WHAT AN HONOR,
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
I'M JUST LIKE EVERY
OTHER DEALER OUT THERE.
THINKING OTHERWISE IS NAIVE
AND DANGEROUS,
ESPECIALLY IF IT
MAKES YOU HESITATE
BEFORE PULLING THE TRIGGER.
THE WORLD WE LIVE IN DOESN'T
HAVE MUCH ROOM FOR KINDNESS.
THE UN HAS A LIST CALLED THE
MILLENNIUM DEVELOPMENT GOALS.
A 189 COUNTRIES WORKING TO END
POVERTY AND SUCH BY 2015.
CONSIDER GOALS TWO AND FOUR.
ACHIEVE UNIVERSAL
PRIMARY EDUCATION
AND DECREASE
THE CHILD MORTALITY RATE.
THESE GOALS ALONE WILL COST
A PROJECTED $220 BILLION.
FAR LESS THAN THE AMOUNT SPENT
ANNUALLY ON WEAPONS WORLDWIDE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
THESE PEOPLE CARE MORE ABOUT WAR
THAN OUR CHILDREN'S FUTURES.
- BUT THAT'S GOOD FOR BUSINESS,
RIGHT?
- AND I SHOULD BE HAPPY MY GOODS
ARE SELLING SO WELL?
YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
IT'S WEIRD, THOUGH.
SEE, BEING AN ARMS DEALER GIVES
ME AN INTERESTING PERSPECTIVE.
I CAN SEE CONTRADICTIONS
OTHERS MISS.
SO I UNDERSTAND
THE WAY THE WORLD WORKS
BETTER THAN
MOST PEOPLE DO.
YOU MAY BELIEVE ME
OR YOU MAY NOT,
BUT HERE'S A QUESTION FOR YOU.
WHAT GROUP OF PEOPLE OWNS
THE MAJORITY OF GUNS?
- MILITARY, DUH.
- SORRY, THAT'S WRONG.
IT'S CIVILIANS.  YEP.
60% OF ALL THE GUNS
IN THE WORLD ARE OWNED
BY ORDINARY CITIZENS.
AS FOR THE REST OF THEM,
37% BELONG
TO VARIOUS MILITARIES
AND A FRACTION TO THE POLICE.
YOU KNOW THOSE REBEL ARMIES
THE MEDIA SALIVATES OVER?
THEY DON'T EVEN POSSESS .1%
OF THE GUNS IN THE WORLD.
REMEMBER WHAT YOU SAID BEFORE?
A NORMAL PERSON WITH A GUN WILL
WIND UP DOING SOMETHING
HE NEVER THOUGHT HIMSELF
CAPABLE OF.
NOBODY IN THIS WORLD CAN TRULY
HOLD HIMSELF SEPARATE
FROM VIOLENCE.
GUNS ARE LITERALLY
WITHIN REACH OF ANYONE.
SADLY, THAT'S WHERE
WE PUT OUR FAITH,
IN BULLETS
RATHER THAN HUMAN KINDNESS.
YOU KNOW, JONAH,
I REALLY DON'T WANT YOU TO DIE
OR ANY OF THE OTHERS, OF COURSE.
- THEN DO US ALL A FAVOR
AND STAY AWAY
FROM ASSASSINS FROM NOW ON.
CATS MAY HAVE NINE LIVES,
BUT I DON'T.
- ( laughs )
SORRY, I DON'T MEAN TO LAUGH.
YOU'RE JUST SO RIGHT.
FORGIVE ME?
- Koko: STOP THERE.
THE SECOND YOU AIM THAT GUN
AT ME, YOU'RE DEAD.
- THIS GUY MUST BE BETTER
THAN THE ONE YOU USED YESTERDAY.
I CAN'T EVEN TELL FOR SURE
WHICH DIRECTION HE'S IN.
FINE, I YIELD.
- YOU DON'T GET IT, DO YOU?
WHAT, YOU THINK THIS
IS SOME COURTLY DUEL?
IT WAS ALWAYS A GAME
OF CHANCE, NOTHING MORE.
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU.
I GUESSED YOU'D WAIT THREE DAYS
AND THEN TRY THE ROOF
AND NOW HERE WE ARE.
MY BET PAID OFF.
A DAY LATER
AND WE MIGHT HAVE GONE,
LEAVING YOU FREE
TO HUNT ME DOWN,
SO THANK YOU
BECAUSE I WANTED TO CHAT.
- HUH?
- CHINATSU,
WHAT IS UP WITH
THE NO PANTIES THING?
- YOU BITCH!
YOU'RE JUST SCREWING WITH ME.
- NO, I'M SERIOUS.
I DON'T EXPECT SOMETHING
FOR NOTHING.
IF YOU TELL ME WHAT I WANT
TO KNOW,
THEN I'LL ANSWER THE QUESTION
YOU ASKED WHEN WE FIRST MET.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY I STAY
IN THIS BUSINESS,
EVEN THOUGH IT WILL PROBABLY
KILL ME IN THE END.
- IT WAS THE FIRST JOB I WORKED
AS PART OF ORCHESTRA.
WE HAD TO CROSS A RIVER
TO GET TO THE TARGET'S HOUSE.
WALKING AROUND IN WET UNDERWEAR
FELT DISGUSTING
SO I DECIDED TO TAKE THEM OFF.
MY AIM WAS UNUSUALLY GOOD
DURING THAT FIGHT.
MAESTRO WAS SO PROUD.
I TOOK OUT MORE GUYS
THAN HE DID.
- NOT WEARING PANTIES
INCREASES YOUR ACCURACY?
( laughing )
- YEAH, PRETTY MUCH.
- AWESOME STORY.  AND NOW?
- YES, I'M FUCKING
WEARING SOME NOW.
- ALL RIGHT, MY TURN.
- YOU'RE ONE FRIGHTENING WOMAN.
- YEAH, BUT I ADMIT,
I DO FIND YOU INTERESTING.
YOU COULD JOIN MY CREW.
YOU WANT TO?
- NO WAY.  I COULDN'T EVEN WAIT
THREE WHOLE DAYS.
I KNOW I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU.
I AM ORCHESTRA.
I AM AN ARTIST.
WHEN I PLAY,
IT IS A SYMPHONY OF DEATH.
DON'T UNDERESTIMATE ME,
ARMS DEALER.
I WILL NEVER WORK FOR YOU.
THE-- THE SKY.
SO BEAUTIFUL.
I NEVER KNEW,
BUT HOW COULD I?
I WAS ALWAYS LOOKING DOWN
AT THE GROUND.
SHE'S A...
MONSTER.
- HUH?  HEY, LUTZ.
YOU WERE WATCHING?
SO YOU SAW THAT NASTY
LITTLE DISPLAY, HUH?
"HOW COULD YOU KILL
A YOUNG GIRL LIKE HER?"
THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT
TO ASK ME, ISN'T IT?
IT'S SIMPLE.
I'VE LOST A LOT OF COMRADES
OVER THE YEARS.
BUT YOU KNOW,
FIVE OF THEM WERE TO A SOLDIER
JUST LIKE THAT CHICKIE.
IT'S A CYCLE.  YOU KILL SOMEONE,
SOMEONE KILLS YOU.
DO ME A FAVOR, WHEN IT'S MY
TURN TO GO, DON'T AVENGE ME.
- SORRY, KID.  IF IT HELPS, YOU
DID MANAGE TO RUIN MY VACATION.
COMMANDER.  RIGHT.
YES, I KNOW IT'S LATE.
I JUST FINISHED KILLING
OFF ORCHESTRA.
ON THE ROOF.
YES, WE SNIPED THEM.
I APPRECIATE IT.
WHAT'S THAT?
OF COURSE, SIR,
I CAN GET YOU A GREAT DEAL
ON A SNIPER INSTRUCTOR.
NOT ONE OF MY TEAM, BUT STILL
QUALITY, I ASSURE YOU.
RIGHT.  GOOD.
PLEASURE DOING BUSINESS
WITH YOU.
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE
IS LOCO, I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS LOCO,
I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪