- Jonah ( thinking ):
I'VE KIND OF NOTICED SOMETHING.
I DON'T EVER SMILE
IN FRONT OF KOKO.
BUT SHE ALWAYS SEEMS
TO HAVE A SMILE ON HER FACE
FOR THE REST OF US,
LIKE SHE'S KEEPING
EVERYTHING ELSE HIDDEN.
- HEY.
AWESOME.  THANK YOU, JONAH.
IT JUST DIED.
AND I SWEAR, I HAVEN'T EVEN
BEEN USING IT VERY LONG TODAY.
MAYBE IT'S TIME
FOR A NEW ONE.
- NO PROBLEM.
DON'T WORRY.
- ( laughs )
- SO FAR,
I'VE HAD A PRETTY GOOD TIME.
I KNOW THAT KOKO IS REALLY GOOD
AT WHAT SHE DOES.
BUT SOMETIMES IT FEELS
LIKE SHE'S BARRELING FULL-SPEED
DOWN A HILL AND COULD FALL
ON HER FACE AT ANY TIME.
ANYTHING ELSE?
- NO, I'M GOOD.
GO PLAY, HAVE FUN.
I'LL JOIN YOU AS SOON
AS I'M DONE, I PROMISE.
- ( laughs )
- HEY, LOOK WHO DECIDED
TO JUST DROP IN.
- IT'S THROW-A-JONAH!
WHO CAN CHUCK HIM THE FARTHEST?
- ( laughs )
SUCH A CUTIE.
- KOKO!
THE WATER'S LOVELY.
- Koko:
I'LL BE DONE IN A SEC.
- ( grunting )
- DAMN, UGO!
- YEAH, RIGHT?
- ( laughs )
- CAREFUL.
YOU DON'T WANNA HURT
OUR SWEET LITTLE JONAH, DO YA?
- HERE I AM,
TRAVELING WITH AN ARMS DEALER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Tojo: MAN, LUTZ,
WOULD YA LOOK AT HER?
THAT IS ONE HOT BODY.
- YEAH.
HER TITS ARE GREAT AS EVER.
BUT KEEP IT TO YOURSELF,
WILL YA?
I DON'T WANNA
GET CAUGHT LOOKIN' AT HER.
IT'S A CAPITAL SENTENCE--
DEATH BY KNIFE.
- YEAH.
JUST OUR FRIGGIN' LUCK, HUH?
THAT KILLER BODY
BELONGS TO AN ACTUAL KILLER.
HERE,
JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
WE'LL PUT ON OUR BEST I'M-NOT-
CHECKING-OUT-YOUR-RACK FACES
AND JUST SWIM AROUND, LAUGHING
AND CHATTIN' LIKE NORMAL.
KEEP IT COOL AND CASUAL.
THAT'S STEP ONE, ANYWAY.
WE'LL MOVE ON FROM THERE.
WHAT THE HELL IS R DOING?
OILY BASTARD BEAT US TO HER.
COMPLIMENTING THAT TATTOO
FROM HER ARMY DAYS.
SMOOTH.
- IT'S TEXTBOOK.
- AW!  AND NOW THE FRIENDLY
MASSAGE MANEUVER.
I KNOW WHERE THIS IS GOING.
- WHOA, HE TOUCHED ONE?
WHAT'S HE THINKING?
- HE'S EITHER GOT BALLS OF STEEL
OR A DEATH WISH.
- WATCH YOURSELF, R.
THESE TITS BELONG TO TWO PEOPLE!
ME AND KOKO!
- LIKE I CARE! I'VE GOT A CHICK
WAITING IN EVERY PORT.
- TO EACH HIS OWN.
NOT THE LAST WORDS I'D CHOOSE.
- DAMN. HE GOT TOSSED
EVEN FARTHER THAN JONAH DID.
- WE NEED A MEDIC OVER HERE!
- MEDIC!  MEDIC!
- Koko: CAREFUL, JONAH.
AT THIS RATE, YOU'RE GONNA
DRIFT ALL THE WAY TO ITALY.
- KOKO, HEY.
DIDN'T KNOW I WAS SO FAR OUT.
- YOU SHOULD NEVER UNDERESTIMATE
THE OCEAN.
A MERMAID PULLED YOU OUT HERE.
I THINK
SHE HAS A CRUSH ON YOU.
( laughs )
TOO BAD FOR HER.
I WON'T LET THE MERFOLK
HAVE YOU.
YOU BELONG TO ONLY ME, JONAH.
RIGHT?
- ( stomach grumbling )
- JUST HANG IN THERE
FOR ANOTHER 30 MINUTES.
AFTER SCIENCE,
IT'LL BE CHOW TIME.
ON A SUNNY DAY LIKE THIS,
MY KIDS'D BE SOUND ASLEEP
RIGHT AFTER DINNER.
DURING DINNER, MAYBE.
- I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD A FAMILY.
- YEAH, I'M A LUCKY MAN.
I'VE GOT A WIFE, A SON,
AND A DAUGHTER BACK HOME.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE 'EM?
MY KIDS ARE JUST
A LITTLE YOUNGER THAN YOU.
- THEY'RE CUTE.
- I KNOW.
THEY LOOK LIKE ME, RIGHT?
ESPECIALLY AROUND THE NOSE.
- NO. LUCKILY,
THEY LOOK LIKE THEIR MOTHER.
- ( laughs )
- YOU KNOW, I'M THE ONLY ONE
IN THE UNIT WITH A FAMILY.
WELL, UNLESS YOU COUNT LEHM
AND HIS MULTIPLE DIVORCES.
- HUH?  REALLY?
- A-CHOO!
- YAH!  WOULD IT REALLY
HAVE BEEN SO HARD
TO SNEEZE IN
THE OTHER DIRECTION?
- MY BAD.
- SO HE JUST KEEPS GETTING
MARRIED? TO HOW MANY WOMEN?
- JUST ONE. SAME GIRL OVER AND
OVER. YOU ACTUALLY KNOW HER.
- EH?
- IT'S CHEQUITA.
ORIGINALLY, THEY BOTH WORKED
AS PERSONAL SECURITY
FOR KOKO'S FATHER,
FLOYD HEKMATYAR.
- CHEQUITA AND LEHM, HUH?
- CAN YOU IMAGINE?
WHO'D WANNA MESS WITH THOSE TWO?
TALK ABOUT DEADLY.
YOU'LL SEE.
WE'RE A TEAM,
BUT WE'RE EACH
STILL OUR OWN PERSON.
FOR ALL THAT WE'RE TOGETHER NOW,
WE'VE GOT OUR OWN VARIED PASTS.
NOW BACK TO SCIENCE.
- AND YOU?
- HUH?
- WHAT TYPE OF SOLDIER
DID YOU USED TO BE?
- WHO, ME?
UNLIKE SOME OF THE OTHER GUYS,
I WASN'T AN ELITE OFFICER.
JUST YOUR TYPICAL GRUNT SOLDIER,
REALLY.
I WAS ASSIGNED
TO AN ARTILLERY UNIT.
MAN, THE GUNS I SHOT
WERE SO BIG,
YOU COULD STICK YOUR HEAD
INSIDE OF 'EM.
FORTUNATELY, MY COUNTRY
WAS ENJOYING A TIME OF PEACE.
WE ONLY USED THE GUNS IN DRILLS,
NOT ACTUAL COMBAT.
- YOU WERE LUCKY.
- YEAH,
BUT NOT AS LUCKY AS YOU THINK.
THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT.
IN IT, A SOLDIER WAS LOST.
AND I WAS DISCHARGED.
I WAS DRIFTING AROUND
AFTER THAT.
AND KOKO JUST SO HAPPENED
TO BE IN ASIA.
SHE WAS KIND ENOUGH
TO HIRE ME.
I'M EMBARRASSED TO ADMIT IT,
BUT I LIED TO MY CHILDREN
ABOUT THE DETAILS OF MY NEW JOB.
I TOLD THEM DADDY
HAS TO TRAVEL A LOT NOW
BECAUSE HIS WORK WITH THE ARMY
REQUIRES IT.
I JUST COULDN'T BRING MYSELF
TO SAY,
"I GOT KICKED OUT AND NOW I'M
AN ARMS DEALER'S BODYGUARD."
JUST BETWEEN
YOU AND ME, THOUGH,
WORKING FOR KOKO PAYS A
WHOLE HELL OF A LOT BETTER
THAN BEING IN THE ARMY.
THREE TIMES BETTER, IN FACT.
SO ANYWAY, NOT LONG
AFTER JOINING THE CREW,
I TALKED TO KOKO ABOUT THE LIE
I'D TOLD MY CHILDREN.
- YOU LIED TO YOUR KIDS?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NATURAL.
WHEN YOU GET DOWN TO IT,
OUR JOB IS EVIL.
WHAT KIND OF FOOL
WOULD TAKE PRIDE IN IT?
WITH THAT SAID,
I WANT YOU TO BE CAREFUL
NOT TO LET THE WEIGHT
OF YOUR CONSCIENCE CRUSH YOU.
IF NOTHING ELSE, YOU CAN
TAKE PRIDE IN YOUR TEAMMATES.
NEVER FORGET THAT.
- KOKO ALWAYS SEEMS
TO KNOW WHAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT.
EVEN SO, I WONDER,
WHAT EXACTLY IS HER GRAND PLAN
IN ALL OF THIS?
- ( ringing )
- YEAH?
- Koko: MAO?
- THAT'S ME.
- WE'RE GETTING READY TO EAT.
- WHA--
IT'S CHOW TIME NOW?
HE GOT ME TALKING SO LONG,
WE NEVER GOT AROUND TO CLASS.
- ARE YOU THERE?
- OH, YEAH.
- WELL, HURRY UP.
- RIGHT.  JONAH.
HE'S ALREADY GONE,
OF COURSE.
- Koko: RIGHT, GUYS,
IF YOU'LL TAKE A LOOK AT THE
INFORMATION IN FRONT OF YOU,
YOU'LL SEE IT'S TIME
FOR AN AIR DELIVERY.
- Lehm: THINGS WORK BETTER FOR
KOKO WHEN THERE'S NO AIR TRAVEL.
REALLY, FLYING WITH HER
IS NEVER A GOOD EXPERIENCE.
- HEY, WATCH IT, LEHM.
JINXES LIKE THAT
ARE NOTHING MORE
THAN MANIFESTATIONS
OF YOUR SUBCONSCIOUS ANXIETY.
YOU'VE GOT YOUR BRAIN
ALL CONVINCED THAT
SOMETHING IS GOING TO
GO WRONG, AND SO IT DOES.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
YOU JUST HAVE TO LET IT GO.
- DIDN'T SHE JUST JINX US?
- ( laughs )
- GRRR!  FINE.
YOU'LL SEE.
EVERYTHING'S GONNA GO
SMOOTHLY ON THIS FLIGHT
AND THEN
YOU'LL BE EATING YOUR WORDS.
- YEAH, SURE.
- Man: OCCASIONALLY,
H.C.L.I. DELIVERS PEOPLE
AS WELL AS PRODUCTS.
YOUR DESTINATION
IS AUTONOMOUS DISTRICT X
IN THE REPUBLIC OF T.
TAKE YOUR SHIPMENT
TO PLANINA AIRPORT THERE.
WE WANNA MAKE SURE
THEY GET TO THE SAFE HOUSE
WITHOUT THE
LOCAL TROOPS KNOWING.
THEY'RE WITH
ONE OF THOSE N.G.O.s
THAT FLIES THEIR PEOPLE
ALL OVER THE DAMN WORLD.
O.D.H., THAT'S IT--
OUTSPOKEN DOCTORS FOR HUMANITY.
- MMM.
THEY'VE BEEN DENIED ENTRY,
THOUGH?
THE REPUBLIC DOESN'T WANT THEM?
- THAT IS CORRECT.
- I'M SURE
I'VE MISREAD THE SITUATION,
BUT LET ME JUST DOUBLE CHECK.
WE'RE SITTING
ON AN ENORMOUS POWDER KEG HERE,
AND WHAT YOU WANT IS FOR US ALL
TO LIGHT UP CIGARETTES?
- THEY'VE ALREADY PAID
60% OF THE FEE.
H.C.L.I. HEADQUARTERS WILL BE
WIRED THE REST UPON COMPLETION.
SAFE TRAVELS.
- STUPID MORON-HEAD
JERK FACE!
- Lehm: STILL THINK
IT'S ALL IN MY HEAD, KOKO?
( laughs )
- ( sighs )
- CAPTAIN!  UGO!
WE'RE ADDING CARGO.
- Both: WE ARE?
- 700 KILOGRAMS
WORTH OF DOCTORS.
- Both: WE CAN JUST
BARELY MANAGE THAT.
- MS. HEKMATYAR, I WANT TO
TELL YOU HOW GRATEFUL WE ARE.
- ABOUT THAT,
DR. RIVIERE,
YOU DO KNOW
THAT I'M AN ARMS DEALER?
- YES, I'M AWARE. STILL, WE
APPRECIATE YOU TRANSPORTING US.
- I WANT YOU ALL TO UNDERSTAND,
YOU ARE CARGO, NOT PASSENGERS.
IF I HAVE TO, I WILL SHOVE YOU
IN A SHIPPING CONTAINER.
- WE'RE USED TO IT.
- ( all laugh )
- ALL RIGHT, O.D.H.,
PREPARE FOR IMMEDIATE DEPARTURE.
- All: AYE-AYE, SIR.
- HUMANITARIAN RELIEF GROUP,
HUH?
ISN'T THEIR WORK
BASICALLY, LIKE,
THE OPPOSITE OF OURS?
- JONAH, HAVE YOU MET
NON-PROFIT GUYS BEFORE,
LIKE THEM?
- YEAH, I'VE COME ACROSS PEOPLE
FROM THE RED CROSS BEFORE,
BUT THESE GUYS ARE GIVIN' OFF
A TOTALLY DIFFERENT VIBE.
- YEAH, I AGREE.
- Lutz: THEY SEEM MORE
LIKE A MILITARY UNIT THAN WE DO.
- THAT'S IT, KEEP IT MOVING.
- Lutz: CHECK OUT THEIR CHIEF.
LOOKS LIKE SOME KIND
OF BAD-ASS MERCENARY TO ME.
- ( laughs )
- SORRY TO INTERRUPT
WHAT IS OBVIOUSLY A GOOD TIME.
BUT GET YOUR LAZY ASSES IN GEAR
AND BOARD THE DAMN PLANE!
- HEY.
- MMM?
- YOU SEEM AWFULLY YOUNG.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- JONATHAN MAR.
AND WHO ARE YOU?
- MY NAME'S MARGARET MESSNER.
YOU CAN CALL ME MAGGIE.
- UH, MAGGIE?
COOL, PEOPLE CALL ME JONAH.
- THIS IS GOING REALLY WELL.
SMOOTH SAILING SO FAR.
HMM.  SEE, LEHM?
I TOLD YOU I WASN'T A JINX
WHEN IT CAME TO FLYING.
SO THERE.
- ( static)
- Koko: JONAH,
COME CHECK OUT THE COCKPIT.
- ON MY WAY.
- JONAH.
PRETTY CUTE
FOR A CHILD SOLDIER, HUH?
- NOT THE FIRST ONE YOU'VE MET?
- NO.
I'VE MET TOO MANY.
THEY SEND KIDS TO WAR
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
- JONAH, OVER HERE.
COME ON DOWN.
MIGHT BE CRAMPED, THOUGH.
I'LL BET
YOU'VE NEVER LOOKED
OUT THE NOSE
OF AN AIRPLANE BEFORE.
- WHOA.
IT'S SO BIG.
SO THIS IS WHAT THE WORLD
LOOKS LIKE.
- Riviere: THE BALKANS
ARE EUROPE'S MUNITIONS MAGAZINE.
YOU'LL SEE.  THE DISTRICT
WE'RE HEADED TO NOW?
IT'S A GREAT EXAMPLE.
VARIOUS NATIONALITIES CONSIDER
DISTRICT X THEIR LOST HOME.
WARS OVER THIS PIECE OF LAND
HAVE KEPT IT A CONSTANT HELL ON
EARTH SINCE THE 14th CENTURY.
IT IS SAID THAT THE TERM
"ETHNIC CLEANSING" ORIGINATES
FROM THE DESCRIPTION OF THE
ATROCITIES PERPETRATED HERE.
OF COURSE, IT WASN'T LONG
BEFORE THE PEOPLE
WHO SO REVILED
THE REPUBLIC'S ACTIONS
BEGAN USING
THE SAME TACTICS THEMSELVES.
WHEN THE MILITIA RISES
TO THE STATUS OF OFFICIAL ARMY,
THERE IS NO REIGNING IN
THE VIOLENCE.
A MAN
CALLED DRAGAN NIKOLAEVICH
IS THE HEAD OF THE MILITIA
GROUP, THE BALKAN DRAGONS.
BOTH THE GROUP AND ITS LEADER
ARE ALSO KNOWN AS BALDRA.
HIS FATHER IS A GENERAL
IN THE REPUBLIC'S ARMY.
BY THE AGE OF 10,
BALDRA WAS ALREADY A DELINQUENT.
IN HIS 20s, HE BEGAN TRAVELING
THROUGH WESTERN EUROPE.
HIS CRIMES THERE
RANGED FROM ROBBERY TO MURDER.
BUT EVERY TIME HE WAS CAUGHT,
HIS FATHER USED HIS POLITICAL
CONNECTIONS TO BAIL HIS SON OUT.
BALDRA IS IN HIS 50s NOW,
AND AS THE LEADER
OF THE MILITIA,
HIS CRIMES
ARE GREATER THAN EVER.
WE'RE DEALING WITH
WORLD-CLASS SCUM HERE.
MS. HEKMATYAR'S BUSINESS
SEEMS TO BE WITH THE REPUBLIC'S
OFFICIAL ARMY.
BUT IF BALDRA
DECIDES TO INVOLVE HIS MILITIA,
THINGS'LL GET UGLY FAST.
FOR US,
AND FOR HER COMPANY AS WELL.
EVEN SO, IT DOESN'T CHANGE
WHAT WE'VE COME HERE TO DO!
WE WILL HELP ANYONE WE CAN
AND TELL THE WORLD WHAT WE SEE!
WON'T WE?
- All: AYE AYE, SIR.
- WOW.
THEIR DEDICATION TO THE CAUSE
IS PRETTY IMPRESSIVE.
- IF YOU THINK WHAT THEY DO
IS SO NOBLE, LUTZ,
WHY DON'T YOU
JOIN UP WITH THEM?
- ( laughs )
- WHAT THE HELL'S THAT MEAN?
YOU SAYIN' YOU DON'T
THINK I COULD HACK IT?
- WE SHOULD BE THERE SOON.
MAGGIE, COME HERE.
- WHAT IS IT?
- GATHER YOUR CREW TOGETHER.
YOU SHOULD ALL HIDE UNDER THIS
TARP SO YOU LOOK LIKE CARGO.
WE'RE NOT UNLOADING
THIS CONTAINER,
SO IT SHOULD BE A SAFE SPOT.
THAT WAY THE SOLDIERS
WON'T FIND YOU.
- IF THEY DO?
- IT SHOULDN'T COME TO THAT.
- I CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH
FOR MAKING THIS DELIVERY,
MS. HEKMATYAR.
YOU'RE A LIFESAVER.
I AM SO GLAD
WE WENT WITH YOUR COMPANY.
- THERE'S NO NEED TO THANK ME,
CAPTAIN.
INDEED, YOU HAVE MY THANKS
FOR DOING BUSINESS
WITH ME AND H.C.L.I.
- JUST ONE MORE THING.
I UNDERSTAND THAT USUALLY
YOU CARRY MORE THAN ENOUGH
CARGO TO FILL AN ORDER
AND THAT YOU'LL PART
WITH THE EXCESS GOODS
IF THE PRICE IS RIGHT.
- I'M AFRAID I HAVE
TO DISAPPOINT YOU, CAPTAIN.
WHILE THAT IS OFTEN TRUE WHEN
WE MAKE MARITIME DELIVERIES,
THE SIZE OF
YOUR ORDER PUT US AT
MAXIMUM WEIGHT
FOR DELIVERY BY AIR.
- AH. I HAD NOT
THOUGHT OF THAT.
- MAO?
- UH?
HEY, KOKO. SO, THE ORDER
THIS TIME WAS ARTILLERY
FOR 122mm CANNONS, HUH?
- YEP.
FEELING NOSTALGIC?
- NAH NAH.
THOUGH, I DID USED TO SHOOT
THESE BABIES AN AWFUL LOT.
- WE'LL BE GETTING OUT OF HERE
AS SOON AS WE'RE
DONE WITH THE PAPERWORK.
THERE'S SOMETHING OFF
ABOUT THIS BASE,
AND I DON'T LIKE IT.
- ( tires squeal )
- LETTING OUR GUESTS
WANDER WHEREVER THEY PLEASE?
WHAT KIND OF DUMBASS
ARE YOU, CAPTAIN?
MS. HEKMATYAR. PLEASURE TO
MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
TO THINK,
I VERY NEARLY MISSED YOU.
I WILL JUST CUT STRAIGHT
TO THE CHASE, YES?
YOU HAVE SOMETHING
ONBOARD THAT YOU'RE NOT
SUPPOSED TO HAVE. SHOW ME.
- MR. NIKOLAEVICH.
( thinking ) BALDRA.
- I DON'T LIKE
REPEATING MYSELF.
LET ME MAKE THIS EASY FOR YOU.
I KNOW FULL WELL
YOU'VE GOT TEN DOCTORS STASHED
IN THAT AIRCRAFT LIKE CARGO.
UNLOAD THEM IMMEDIATELY!
- I'M SORRY,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
AND IT WOULDN'T MATTER
IF I DID,
BECAUSE YOU ARE NOT MY CLIENT
IN THIS TRANSACTION.
THAT ROLE BELONGS
TO THE REPUBLIC ARMY.
SO, YOU SEE, I'M NOT ABOUT
TO DISCUSS MY CARGO,
LET ALONE SHOW IT TO YOU.
- YOU'RE GIVING ME LIP?
I COULD FUCKING KILL YOU.
- I WOULDN'T DO ANYTHING
QUITE SO RASH IF I WERE YOU.
THAT 123 CUBIC METER HOLD
RIGHT THERE IS MY KINGDOM.
ENTRY VISAS AREN'T CHEAP,
AND I CHOOSE MY GUESTS.
- ARGH!  WASTE OF TIME.
CAPTAIN!  CAPTAIN!
- MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY.
- ( grunting )
- WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
BRINGING THIS BITCH HERE?
YOU'RE MORE THAN JUST A DUMBASS!
YOU DISGUST ME.
THIS BROKE.
GET ME A NEW ONE.
- Man: HERE YOU ARE, SIR.
- COLONEL NIKOLAEVICH,
THERE IS NO REASON WE NEED
TO MAKE THIS INTO A BIG DEAL.
H.C.L.I. IS JUST--
- YOU GET MORE STUPID EVERY
TIME YOU OPEN YOUR MOUTH.
DON'T MAKE THIS INTO A BIG DEAL?
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT.
- UM, WELL, SON OF A BITCH.
THE BOYS IN BERETS
ARE MULTIPLYING.
- ( laughs )
I AM SORRY FOR THAT
UNGENTLEMANLY DISPLAY.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT US.
I JUST HOPE YOUR FACE IS OKAY.
YOU GUYS ARE CALLED
THE BALKAN ELITE, AREN'T YOU?
SO WHY DO YOU LET THE MILITIA
GET AWAY WITH THIS KIND OF SHIT?
- THAT WEASEL IS SOMETHING
OF A HERO IN THIS AREA.
THERE IS NOT MUCH
I CAN DO TO STOP IT.
AND HE GROWS MORE POWERFUL
EVERY DAY.
I HAVE ORDERED
ALL MY SOLDIERS TO WITHDRAW.
I AM NOT GOING TO ASK
WHAT YOU HAVE INSIDE THE HOLD.
BUT I RECOMMEND YOU LEAVE
AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
- THANK YOU, CAPTAIN,
THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
YOU'RE A DELIGHTFUL MAN,
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
- DON'T THINK YOU'RE GETTING OFF
THAT EASILY.
- ( all cock guns )
THOSE DOCTORS
YOU'VE BROUGHT ARE GONNA DIE.
AND WHO DOESN'T
LIKE A GOOD SNUFF FILM?
BEST WAY TO SPREAD YOUR MESSAGE
THESE DAYS
IS PUTTING REAL FOOTAGE
ON THE INTERNET.
- I'LL WARN YOU ONE MORE TIME,
BALDRA--
I WOULD ADVISE YOU
AGAINST DOING ANYTHING RASH.
- SO THAT'S BALDRA.
- THINGS GOT HAIRY THE SECOND
HE SET FOOT ON THE TARMAC.
- IT SHOULDN'T COME TO THAT.
- HE KNOWS WE'RE HERE
AND NOW WE'RE ALL IN DANGER.
INCLUDING YOU, LITTLE JONAH.
- HOLD MY PLACE.
I'M GONNA GO TAKE A LEAK.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA?
YOU KNOW FULL WELL
WHAT BALDRA IS CAPABLE OF.
DO YOU HONESTLY THINK
YOU CAN REASON WITH THAT MANIAC?
- THIS ISN'T JUST ABOUT US.
WE'RE CAUSING PROBLEMS
FOR MS. HEKMATYAR.
I CAN'T SIT HERE
PRETENDING TO BE CARGO.
WE'VE WORKED THINGS
OUT WITH ALL SORTS OF
MILITARIES IN THE PAST.
YOU GUYS WAIT HERE.
- DON'T-- NO.
( thinking ) WHAT NOW?
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
- HEY, WHAT ARE--
- GET BACK, DOCTOR. YOU KNOW
YOU SHOULDN'T BE OUT HERE.
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
- ( grunts )
- HELLO, MR. BALDRA.
I AM HERE ON BEHALF OF
OUTSPOKEN DOCTORS FOR HUMANITY.
I AM THE CHIEF DOCTOR,
RIVIERE.
MS. HEKMATYAR BROUGHT ME HERE
BECAUSE I PRESSURED
HER TO DO SO.
I'D LIKE TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
WILL YOU PLEASE HEAR ME OUT?
- SURE.
- ( fires )
- ( thinking ) GUNFIRE?
- PLEASE, DOCTOR,
I KNOW WHAT YOU DO.
YOU PATCH UP
THE PEOPLE I SHOOT.
AND THAT MAKES YOU MY ENEMY.
- AHH!
- PLEASE, NO.
- HEY.
STOP SQUIRMING.
- THAT'S ENOUGH SHOOTING
FOR TODAY.
YOU DON'T NEED THAT GUN
ANYMORE.
JUST STAND THERE QUIETLY
AND BEHAVE YOURSELF.
YOU CAN DO THAT, RIGHT?
- YOU BASTARD!
NOBODY SPEAKS LIKE THAT
TO BALDR-- AH!
- WHATCHA WANT US TO DO NOW,
BOSS?
- WE'VE PRETTY MUCH RUN OUT
OF OPTIONS AT THIS POINT.
NEW ORDERS-- ELIMINATE THE
BALKAN DRAGON MILITIA!
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪