- DAMN IT!
I CAN'T GET THROUGH TO THEM.
IS THE SIGNAL BEING JAMMED?
DON'T SAY "MAYBE."
MAYBE DOESN'T CUT IT.
IDENTIFY THE PROBLEM NOW.
- LOOK OUT, WORLD.
THE LITTLE LADY
IS PISSED OFF AGAIN.
- THOSE IDIOTS
AT HQ ARE USELESS.
I'M SO SICK OF THIS SHIT.
HOW ARE WE GOING TO MEET UP
WITH VALMET AND TOJO
IF I CAN'T REACH THEM?
AND SOMETHING ELSE
I WANT TO KNOW.
WHO ARE THOSE GUYS?
- ( theme music playing )
- Lehm: THAT'S ONE OF
THE BORDER POLICE'S RIDES.
HOW DO WE PLAY IT?
- Koko: DON'T BOTHER STOPPING.
IF THEY WANNA PIT AN LAV AGAINST
A 20-TON TRUCK--
- ( screaming )
- ( tires screeching )
AMBUSH.  DAMN!
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET BACK HERE.
- ( sighs )
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?!
- ( laughs ) THEY'RE FIGHTING
FOR THAT PIPELINE.
- WE LANDED OURSELVES SMACK
IN THE MIDDLE OF A BATTLEFIELD.
BUT HEY, AT LEAST
THAT EXPLAINS
WHY THE PHONE
WASN'T WORKING RIGHT.
CHECK IT OUT, WE GOT GMS MOBILE
PHONE BASE STATIONS,
RELAY TOWERS AND MICROWAVE
TRANSMISSION SITES,
ALL BLOWN UP BY WHOEVER
GOT THERE FIRST.
CRAP LIKE THIS GOES DOWN,
BOTH SIDES WANT
TO CONTROL INFORMATION,
WHICH IS WHAT I MEANT
ABOUT THE SAT-PHONE.
COVERT WAR EQUALS
TOTAL BLACKOUT.
- HMM.  YOU KNOW AN AWFUL LOT
ABOUT THIS, LEHM.
- I GUESS.
- Man: WE GOT EYES
ON TWO HEAVY LOAD TRUCKS
AND A SQUAD EQUIPPED
WITH SMALL ARMS.
BODYGUARDS, MOST LIKELY.
AND A WOMAN HAVING
SOME KIND OF SEIZURE.
- Man #2: THAT'S OUR DEALER.
HOLD FIRE.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, BOYS.
WE'RE NOT THE ENEMY.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE
US FRIENDS, THOUGH.
- Man: I'M GLAD YOU COULD
MAKE IT, MS. HEKMATYAR.
IT'S A PLEASURE.
I MUST SAY, YOU'RE A LOT
YOUNGER THAN I EXPECTED.
- NICE TO MEET YOU,
MAJOR POLLACK.
- SORRY IF MY MEN WERE
A LITTLE ROUGH.
THEY'RE KIND OF ON EDGE.
I'M GLAD TO SEE ALL EIGHT
ANTI-AIRCRAFT MISSILES MADE IT,
AS WE AGREED.
- OF COURSE, MAJOR.
- NOW IF YOU WOULD JUST SIGN--
- NO NEED TO RUSH, IS THERE?
GO ON, PULL UP A CHAIR.
- SO TELL ME,
WHEN DID THE SHIT HIT THE FAN?
- JUST EIGHT HOURS AGO.
- I THOUGHT LIEUTENANT COLONEL
GRANT WAS TAKING THIS DELIVERY.
- WELL, THINGS CHANGE.
NOT EVERYONE HAS THE STOMACH
FOR THIS KIND OF FIGHTING.
SO LET'S JUST FORGET ALL
ABOUT THE LIEUTENANT COLONEL.
- DAMN.
THIS IS GONNA GET UGLY SOON.
VERY UGLY.  THINGS ARE VOLATILE
ENOUGH HERE ALREADY,
AND NOW THIS GUY WANTS
EVEN MORE WEAPONS.
HE'LL NEVER BE SATISFIED.
- WAIT FOR IT.
- HERE YOU GO.
THE ORDER'S COMPLETE.
BUT THERE MAY BE SOMETHING
ELSE YOU CAN DO FOR ME.
- THERE IT IS.
- Woman: KOKO?
( laughing )
I THOUGHT THAT WAS YOU.
- HEY, GIRL, LONG TIME NO SEE.
- MILDO.
AND LOU'S WITH YOU.
- HEY, WHERE'S VALMET HIDING?
- SHE'S NOT WITH US ON THIS RUN.
BUT WITH THE TWO OF YOU HERE,
THAT'S GOTTA MEAN...
- WELL, KOKO HEKMATYAR.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
- PRESIDENT CURRY
OF ENGLAND'S CCAT.
"COINCIDENCE" MY ASS.
- HELP YOU WITH SOMETHING?
- WHO'S THIS CHARMING LAD?
A NEW RECRUIT?
( laughs ) AW, THAT'S CLASSIC.
- WHAT'S MR. CURRY HAVE
FOR YOU?
- STINGER MISSILES.
- NEW WARHEADS
WITH REFURBISHED LAUNCHERS.
WE ACQUIRED 'EM FROM SUPPLIERS
IN EASTERN EUROPE.
ONCE THEY'RE OPERATIONAL,
WE'LL GET TO WATCH
AS ATTACK HELIS DROP
LIKE MOSQUITOES,
JUST LIKE THE GOOD OLD DAYS.
- RIGHT.  HE'S GETTING
OUT OF HERE AS SOON AS HE CAN.
- THEY'RE POWERFUL,
PLENTIFUL AND INEXPENSIVE.
PRECISELY THE KIND OF GOODS
OUR CUSTOMERS LOOK FOR.
- WELL, THIS HAS BEEN RIVETING,
BUT NOW THAT OUR CONTRACT
HAS BEEN FULFILLED,
WE'LL BE ON OUR WAY--
- WE'RE NOT DONE.
I NEED SOMETHING ELSE.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- A NEW RADAR UNIT.
MY RADAR SITE WAS TAKEN OUT
IN AN AIR RAID.
I NEED A BATTLEFIELD RADAR
TO REPLACE IT.
SOMETHING OF THAT SIZE
IS BEYOND MY CAPABILITIES.
- THAT'S NOT THE KIND OF
THING I CARRY WITH ME--
- BUT SURELY YOU CAN GET ONE.
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE.
YOUR OWN FATHER,
MR. FLOYD HEKMATYAR,
IS A NAVY GIANT.
IT'S NO SECRET THAT A SIZABLE
CHUNK OF HCLI'S
NAVAL WEAPONS SALES
IN EUROPE AND AFRICA
ARE PERSONALLY OVERSEEN BY YOU.
YOU DON'T
EXPECT US TO BELIEVE
YOU CAN'T GET HOLD
OF A SIMPLE RADAR UNIT.
- YOU OLD FART.
DON'T THINK I CAN'T SEE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
NOPE, NOT HAPPENING.
TOO BAD.  SO SAD.
- WHAT THE BLOODY HELL?
- CAN'T HELP.  GOTTA GO.
- YOU'RE NOT LEAVING YET.
RIGHT, MEN?
- YOU HAVE YOUR ANSWER.  TELL
YOUR GUYS TO BACK THE HELL OFF.
- LUTZ, ENOUGH!
( laughs )
LET'S ALL SETTLE DOWN.
NO REASON THIS HAS
TO GO ALL TARANTINO.
I'VE UNDERESTIMATED YOU,
MAJOR POLLACK.
YOU'RE FEISTIER THAN YOU LOOK.
YOU'VE ORCHESTRATED
AN INFORMATION BLACKOUT.
I'LL BET YOUR INFANTRY EVEN
HAS ORDERS TO KILL ANY CIVILIAN
OR JOURNALIST WHO TRIES
TO FLEE OVER THE PASS.
YOU'RE DESPERATE TO KEEP
THIS BATTLE FOR
THE PIPELINE A SECRET.
YOU INTEND TO KEEP IT
FOR YOURSELF.
- YOU MAKE IT SOUND SO INSIDIOUS
WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT WAY.
( laughs ) YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT
ONE THING, THOUGH.
A SOLDIER DOES EARN HIS PAYCHECK
BY KILLING PEOPLE.
AND AS IT HAPPENS,
MY SOLDIERS ARE VERY WELL PAID.
THEY HAVE A JOB TO DO.
IT'S MY TASK TO GET
THEM THE MATERIALS
THEY NEED TO DO THAT JOB.
YOU CAN AND WILL GET
ME WHAT I NEED.
THAT IS NOT A REQUEST.
NOW YOU GO SEE ABOUT
GETTING MY RADAR UNIT.
I'VE GOT SOME THINGS
TO TAKE CARE OF.
OF COURSE, YOU'LL BE WELL
COMPENSATED WHEN THIS IS OVER.
- THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE, LAD,
BUT I GUESS THE STORM'S PASSED.
YEAH?
- GOODNESS.
PRICKLY FELLOW AND DANGEROUS,
TOO, I'D WAGER.
- HE'S NOTHING.  WHY DON'T YOU
RUN ALONG HOME NOW?
- TA.
- SO WHERE DO WE GO FROM HERE?
- WE'VE GOT AN ORDER TO FILL.
- All: AHH.
- WE NEED TO LOCATE
VALMET AND TOJO.
ACCORDING TO MY INTEL, THIS ARMY
IS JUST ABOUT OUT OF FUNDS.
HE'D NEVER COME
RIGHT OUT AND SAY IT,
BUT IT'S CLEAR HE ONLY INTENDS
TO PAY UP IF HIS SIDE WINS.
I AM NOT A BANK.
I'M KOKO HEKMATYAR.
I NEVER HAVE NOR WILL
ACCEPT CREDIT!
- All: AHH.
- ( gunfire )
- Valmet: I DON'T LIKE THIS.
KOKO'S INSTRUCTIONS
WERE TO WAIT FOR HER
AND THE OTHERS
AT THAT PASS.
- WHAT WERE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
IT'S NOT OUR FAULT THOSE GUYS
DECIDED TO RAID THE AREA.
MAN, THE SUN'S SETTING
AND THEY'RE STILL GOING AT IT.
THAT'S DEDICATION.
- "DEDICATION"?
MORE LIKE STUPIDITY.
RANK AMATEURS.
- OOH!
SOMEBODY'S IN A MOOD, HUH?
- IF YOU WANT,
WE CAN DO A QUICK CHECK
ON THE PASS IN THE MORNING.
THAT ALL RIGHT?
- FINE BY ME.
- AND, HEY, AT LEAST WE FOUND
A PLACE TO CHARGE OUR CELLS.
YEAH, THIS SPOT ISN'T SO BAD.
KIND OF NICE
SLEEPING UNDER THE STARS.
- Pollack: YOU WANT TO CONTACT
HCLI HEADQUARTERS.
YOUR CELLS WILL HAVE RECEPTION
AGAIN ONCE YOU CROSS THE PASS,
EVEN THAT PRECIOUS
IRIDIUM PHONE OF YOURS
ISN'T WORKING HERE, IS IT?
IT JUST SO HAPPENS
THIS IS ONE OF THE ONLY PLACES
IN ALL OF EUROPE
OUT OF ITS RANGE.
- I'M IMPRESSED YOU KNEW I HAD
A SAT-PHONE ON ME,
BUT YEAH, STILL OUT OF RANGE.
- I'LL HAVE TWO OF MY ELITE
SOLDIERS ACCOMPANY YOU.
AS LONG AS YOU'VE
GOT THEM ALONG,
YOU SHOULD MAKE IT THROUGH
THE PASS SAFE ENOUGH.
- GUARD DOGS.
- TAKE CARE.
IT CAN BE TREACHEROUS.
OH, AND IF YOU TRY TO PULL
ANYTHING STUPID I WILL KILL YOU.
- YOU THINK YOU'RE
A REAL BADASS, DON'T YOU?
- REALLY?  TEN MINUTES AND
YOU'RE ALREADY TALKING SMACK?
- PEOPLE LIKE YOU MAKE ME SICK.
HOW MANY DEATHS ARE YOU
RESPONSIBLE FOR?
GUESS WHATEVER
FANCY COLLEGE YOU WENT TO
DIDN'T OFFER
A CLASS ON ETHICS.
- YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
I'M JUST A MERCHANT.
I NEVER WENT TO ANYTHING
RESEMBLING SCHOOL,
LET ALONE A "FANCY COLLEGE."
DESPITE MY LACK OF
FORMAL EDUCATION, HOWEVER,
I KNOW MORE ABOUT WEAPONS
THAN A SHITHEAD LIKE YOU
CAN EVER HOPE TO IN A LIFETIME,
WHICH IS UNFORTUNATE,
BECAUSE
I FIND IT VERY DEPRESSING
TO HAND MY QUALITY MERCHANDISE
OVER TO SOLDIERS NOT WORTHY
OF WIELDING BB GUNS.
AND NOW YOU'VE PISSED ME OFF.
SO YOU MIGHT WANT
TO STOP TALKING.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY,
YOU LITTLE--
- Man:
THIS IS ORIN PASS.
- UGH.  SO FOGGY.
WE MIGHT FINALLY BE ABLE TO GET
THROUGH TO SOMEONE, THOUGH.
YOU DO IT.
TRY CALLING VALMET AND TOJO.
- ( ringing )
- IT'S RINGING.
- WE'VE GOT RECEPTION.
AWESOME!
THOSE ARE MI-24V
HIND Es UP THERE.
THEY'RE RUSSIAN ARMY COPTERS.
WHOA!
EVERYONE, TAKE COVER.
GET AWAY FROM THE CAR.
WHAT'S THEIR TARGET?
IS THE MOUNTAIN INFANTRY NEARBY?
A STINGER.
LOOKS LIKE IT MISSED.  HMM.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- MAJOR POLLACK'S ARMS DEALER.
ARE YOU A PART OF THE UNIT
FIRING THE STINGERS?
- I'M NOT GONNA TELL YOU THAT.
- THEY'RE AS GOOD AS DEAD.
GET YOUR MEN AWAY
FROM THE HINDS.
THOSE THINGS ARE DESIGNED
TO HUNT PEOPLE.
LOOK AT THE SENSOR POD.
THE NORMAL LOW-LIGHT LEVEL
TV "RADUGA-F" HAS BEEN MODIFIED
BY AN EASTERN EUROPEAN THIRD
PARTY WITH A THERMAL SENSOR.
IF HE WANTED TO,
THE PILOT COULD EASILY
PICK UP ON OUR HEAT SIGNATU--
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- THIS CHICK HASN'T STOPPED
SMILING THE ENTIRE TIME.
SHE'S NUTS.
YOU WERE LUCKY THIS TIME.
NOW GET OUT OF HERE.
- I WAS PLANNING TO.
- WHY NOT JUST GO AHEAD
AND SELL HIM WHAT HE WANTS?
- MY GUT.
THIS BATTLE WILL BE SHORT.
TWO DAYS AT THE ABSOLUTE MOST.
IN THE END,
NO ONE WILL REALLY WIN.
RUSSIA'S ALREADY FULL
OF THESE SKIRMISHES,
AND THIS MAJOR HAS A LOT MORE
AMBITION THAN HE CAN AFFORD.
THERE'LL BE PLENTY OF FIGHTS
JUST LIKE THIS ONE
OVER THE NEXT FEW YEARS,
NONE OF THEM WILL BE DECISIVE.
AND NO FACTION
WILL GAIN CONTROL
OF THAT PIPELINE
AND ITS LIQUID GOLD.
PLENTY OF DEALERS WOULD SEE
THIS MESS AND START SALIVATING,
READY TO SELL WEAPONS
LEFT AND RIGHT.
MOST OF THEM, IN FACT,
BUT THAT'S NOT HOW I OPERATE.
AND SO, WE HAVE NO FURTHER
BUSINESS ON THIS BATTLEFIELD.
- WE'RE BASING THIS ALL
ON YOUR GUT?
- YES, BEING A PART
OF THIS TEAM
MEANS TRUSTING MY INTUITION.
THINK YOU CAN HANDLE THAT?
- ( screaming )
- SON OF A BITCH!
- FUCK, MILDO.  WHAT THE BLOODY
HELL WERE YOU THINKING?
- EH, THEY WERE PISSING ME OFF.
ELITE SOLDIERS, MY ASS.
ALL THAT WHINING WAS
GETTING ON ME LAST NERVE.
- DID IT EVEN OCCUR TO YOU,
IN YOUR INFINITE STUPIDITY,
THAT THE MAJOR
SENT THEM ALONG AS ID
TO GET US THROUGH THE PASS?
MY ENTIRE PLAN IS IN SHAMBLES
BECAUSE YOU WERE
GETTING ANNOYED?
DAMN TRIGGER-HAPPY BITCH.
LET ME SEE THE MAP.
- NOTHING FAZES HIM FOR LONG.
I LIKE THAT IN A BOSS.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU
TALKING TO?
- I'M CONFIRMING WITH HQ
WHERE WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO PICK UP THE GOODS.
- WHAT SHOULD WE DO WITH THEM?
- Koko:
NOTHING LETHAL FOR NOW.
TIE THEM UP GOOD.
OH, AND GAG THAT ONE.
HE PISSES ME OFF.  A LOT.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
I WAS FREAKING WORRIED.
- I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
TOO, KOKO.
I COULD DIE HAPPY RIGHT NOW.
- OKAY.
WE GOT EVERYONE?
LET'S GET MOVING.
- WHOOPS.  NOSEBLEED.
- WELL, LOOK WHAT WE GOT HERE.
PUT IT DOWN, LOU.
HEY, IT'S JUST OUR
FRIENDS FROM CCAT.
IT'S ALL GOOD.
WE'RE CLEAR FOR ENTRY.
- NO, ACTUALLY,
IT'S NOT ALL GOOD.
- WELL, MR. CURRY.
FANCY RUNNING INTO YOU HERE.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
THOUGHT YOU'D BE WELL
ON YOUR WAY BACK
TO JOLLY OL' ENGLAND BY NOW.
- BEEN A WHILE, YEAH?
- I GUESS.
- DAMN.  DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW FASCINATING I FIND YOU?
I MEAN, A ONE-EYED
WOMAN SOLDIER.
JUST THE THOUGHT OF YOU FIGHTING
WITH THAT KNIFE MAKES ME SHIVER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY,
YOU WANNA HAVE A GO?
- I THINK I'M GONNA PASS.
SO SORRY.
- MR. CURRY.
- SHUT UP.
YOU'VE DONE ENOUGH ALREADY.
JUST SIT STILL.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW.
- UGH!
DID YOU KILL THE GUARD DOGS
THE MAJOR SENT WITH YOU?
- NO, TYING THEM UP WAS
SUFFICIENT ENOUGH.
- WELL, THAT STUPID WOMAN
KILLED OURS.
ONCE HE KNOWS, HE'S LIKELY
TO SEND GUYS AFTER US.
- MORE THAN LIKELY.
- WHY DON'T WE SEND OUT
A COUPLE OF SCOUTS TO BE SAFE?
- I'M SO SORRY, VALMET.
DO YOU MIND?
- NO PROB.
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE YOU
GET YOUR WISH.
I CAN'T SAY NO TO KOKO.
- SHE'S CHANGED, HASN'T SHE?
I MEAN, THE LAST TIME I SAW HER,
SHE WAS AMAZING,
AND NOW SHE'S
EVEN MORE AMAZING.
- KOKO WAS THE BEST THEN
AND SHE STILL IS.
- LET'S PLAY!
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU
HAVEN'T LOST YOUR EDGE.
NOT THAT I EVER
THOUGHT YOU WOULD.
I CAN'T TOUCH YOU.
YOU'D EXPECT THAT BUM EYE
TO BE A DISADVANTAGE
IN A KNIFE FIGHT,
BUT IT'S NOT.
I THOUGHT THE DARK MIGHT
EVEN THE PLAYING FIELD
A BIT THIS TIME.
SEE, I'VE GOT GREAT
NIGHT VISION,
BUT I'M STILL LOSING.
DAMN YOU!
- HARD TO BELIEVE,
BUT YOUR MOVEMENTS SEEM EVEN
STIFFER THAN LAST TIME,
MILDO.
I LOVE A GOOD KNIFE
MORE THAN ANYONE,
SO I GET WHY YOU WANNA
CARRY SO MANY,
BUT WEIGHING YOURSELF DOWN
WITH THEM MAKES YOU CLUMSY.
EVEN JONAH OUR NEW RECRUIT
SAID YOU WERE COVERED
WITH THE DAMN THINGS.
- JONAH.
SO THAT'S THE KID'S NAME.
- AND YOU THREW THIS KNIFE
THINKING YOU'D MANEUVER
THE FIGHT BACK OVER HERE
AND RECLAIM IT.
YOU'D MAKE A GRAB FOR IT ONCE MY
BACK WAS TURNED OR SOMETHING.
WAS THAT THE PLAN?
SO HOW DID THAT WORK OUT
FOR YOU?
- ( winces )
- WHAT ARE YOU WHINING ABOUT?
ONCE A WEAPON HAS LEFT YOUR
HAND, IT'S GONE FOR GOOD.
ONLY AN IDIOT WOULD RELY
ON GETTING IT BACK.
- FUCK ME.
SHE'S IN LECTURE MODE.
THE GROUP OF TEN IS KOKO
HEKMATYAR AND HER HIRED GUNS.
THE GROUP OF THREE IS
CURRY AND HIS LACKEYS.
KOKO'S GROUP SHOULD
BE YOUR PRIORITY.
I WANT THEM TAKEN CARE OF.
BE QUICK ABOUT IT, THOUGH.
DON'T FORGET THAT WHILE
YOU'RE DEALING WITH THEM,
ORIN PASS AND THE FREEWAY WILL
BE VULNERABLE TO ATTACK.
- ROGER THAT, MAJOR.
- I DON'T LIKE THIS.
IT WAS THE OTHER GROUP
THAT KILLED OUR MEN.
- I'M AWARE OF THAT, THANK YOU.
- YOU MAY WANT TO ADJUST
YOUR LINE OF THINKING, MILDO.
YOU WERE CARRYING ON EARLIER
ABOUT YOUR FASCINATION WITH ME,
BUT I WARN YOU, I AM NOT
SOMEONE YOU WANNA GET CLOSE TO.
- OH, COME ON.
YOUR STORY'S AS COOL AS IT GETS.
AN ELITE U.N. SOLDIER
BETRAYED BY HER OWN
AND STRIPPED OF EVERYTHING,
BUT YOU GOT BACK ON YOUR FEET
AND TRAINED YOUR ASS OFF
UNTIL YOU WERE EVEN
BETTER THAN BEFORE.
- I DON'T REALLY GIVE
A SHIT ABOUT YOU,
BUT I WILL OFFER
THIS PIECE OF ADVICE.
GREAT EXPECTATIONS ONLY LEAD
TO GREAT DISAPPOINTMENT.
- EXPECTATIONS?
I GAVE UP ON THOSE
A WHILE AGO.
PEOPLE WHO DO WHAT WE DO
LEARN EARLY NOT TO EXPECT MUCH
FROM THIS UGLY EMPTY WORLD
BECAUSE WE'RE EMPTY, TOO.
MAYBE IT STARTS THE FIRST TIME
WE HOLD A WEAPON
OR THE FIRST TIME
WE KILL SOMEONE.
WE TELL OURSELVES IT'S TO
PROTECT OUR FAMILY, OUR COUNTRY,
BUT IT DOESN'T TAKE LONG
TO REALIZE THAT'S BULLSHIT.
SO NO, I DON'T EXPECT MUCH.
I THINK THAT BEATING YOU WOULD
MAKE LIFE A LITTLE LESS EMPTY.
- IDIOT.
- ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE OFF THE HOOK FOR NOW,
BUT NEXT TIME, YOUR ASS IS MINE.
- I TAKE IT YOU'VE DETECTED
SCOUTS NEARBY.  HOW FAR?
- FIVE HUNDRED METERS.  TA!
- GOOD CATCH.
WELL, AT LEAST THE POOR GIRL
IS GOOD FOR SOMETHING.
- GUNS AT THE READY, KIDS.
WE'LL GO FIRST AND ESTABLISH
AN ESCAPE ROUTE.
DEPENDING ON WHAT WE'RE
UP AGAINST,
WE MAY BE ABLE TO SUBDUE THEM.
I GUESS I'LL LET YOU OWE
ME ONE THIS TIME.
- YOU ARE BRAVE AND GENEROUS
AS EVER, MISS HEKMATYAR.
- NATURALLY.  LATER, MILDO.
- THERE AREN'T VERY MANY,
BUT THEY HAVE US SURROUNDED.
- ON MY COMMAND, SQUAD.
LOWER YOUR WEAPONS!
- ( laughing )
- WHAT THE--?
- NOW REMOVE YOUR CLIPS
AND FOLD YOUR STOCKS.
POLLACK'S MEN, LISTEN UP.
YOU DON'T WANT US.
THE ONES WHO KILLED
YOUR PALS ARE IN THERE.
- CONNIVING LITTLE TWAT.
DAMN IT.  DAMN IT!
UGH!
- LOOKS LIKE WE'LL BE AWAY FROM
OUR POST FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
PROBABLY WOULDN'T BE TOO HARD
FOR SOMEONE TO SLIP THROUGH
THE BORDER AND HEAD NORTH,
BUT THIS KIND OF STUNT ONLY
WORKS ONCE, LUCKY GIRL.
- HMM.
- ( laughs )
- Koko:
STEP LIVELY, EVERYONE.
I WANT THE HELL OUT
OF THIS KILLING FIELD.
- ( laughing )
- AMUSED, JONAH?  WHAT?
- NOTHING.
JUST FEELS KIND OF WEIRD,
IS ALL.
NEVER LEFT A BATTLEFIELD
WITHOUT FIRING MY WEAPON BEFORE.
- SORRY.
WILL YOU FEEL BETTER
IF I LET YOU SHOOT
A WHOLE BUNCH NEXT TIME?
- ( laughing )
- BETTER BE CAREFUL, JONAH.
YOU'RE GONNA FIGURE OUT REAL
QUICK SHE'S ONLY HALF-JOKING
WHEN SHE SAYS STUFF LIKE THAT.
SHE CAN'T HELP IT.
SHE'S AN ARMS DEALER.
- Pollack: BOTH SIDES WERE
ABLE TO ESCAPE?
IMPRESSIVE, BUT UNFORTUNATE.
BLAME YOU?  NO, NOT AT ALL.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR ACTIONS,
AND I'LL STAND BY THEM.
I'M HERE TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
THAT'S MY JOB.
IT'S OVER AND DONE NOW.
RETURN TO YOUR POST.
IT IS NO COINCIDENCE THE AIR
RAIDS STOPPED
THE SECOND THIS ARRIVED.
IT MAY AS WELL BE A PILE
OF SCRAP METAL FOR ALL THE GOOD
IT'S GONNA DO ME NOW.
JUST MY LUCK.
WORKED OUT FOR HER, THOUGH
THAT WOMAN IS A GRADE-A PSYCHO.
- I KNEW TWO DAYS WAS GENEROUS.
- MA'AM.
- OH, SORRY.  NOTHING.
- HAVE A NICE TRIP.
- THANKS, I WILL.
- ( grunts ) WE MADE IT.
- I'M SO TIRED.
- HUH.  LOOK WHO SURVIVED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO, I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS LOCO,
I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪