[TREYNI]
Greetings, ruler of monsters,
and all of those
who are loyal to him.
Please pardon
my unannounced visit.
I am a dryad
from the Forest of Jura,
please call me Treyni.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
Rimuru Tempest,
as the ruler of monsters,
please help us.
We need you to defeat
the Orc Lord.
♪
Uh, defeat the Orc Lord?
Come on now. Are you serious?
Uh-huh.
That's right.
[BENIMARU]
That's quite the request.
Seeing as you dropped in
out of nowhere,
you won't mind answering
a few questions.
Why did you come to us?
There are stronger races
than the hobgoblins.
Yes, I suppose.
And had the ogres' village
not been destroyed,
I might have gone there.
[ALL gasp]
Though, even if
that were not the case,
I can no longer ignore a certain
individual's existence.
If our settlement were to come
under attack from the orcs,
we couldn't possibly
fend them off alone.
That's why I came here.
To request assistance
from someone strong.
You're mean the Orc Lord
really exists?
Until now, it was only a theory
we'd come up with.
[TREYNI] Well, the dryads
have knowledge
of essentially everything
that happens in this forest.
Believe me, he is real.
[ALL gasp]
Hmm?
If she acknowledges it...
That means it's all true.
Hmm.
Give me some time to answer.
Backing the Kijin is one thing,
but taking on an Orc Lord
is different story.
I need a little more
information before I decide.
After all,
I am the one in charge.
[gasps]
Hmm.
[groaning softly]
[RIMURU]
Okay, back to business.
So, let's talk about
the orcs a bit.
Does anyone know
what they could be after?
[SHUNA] Actually, I think
I might have an idea about that.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
Uh, Souei,
about our old village,
did you investigate it?
Yes.
And judging by your tone,
it's bad.
You didn't find anything?
-[SOUEI] Correct.
-Huh?
There was nothing there.
Not one of theirs.
And none of ours.
Wait, no what?
Corpses.
[gasps]
We wondered how they were
getting supplies
for such a large army.
How they could feed
200,000 orcs.
Are you saying
they ate the dead?
It's a Unique Skill.
Called "Starved."
[RIMURU]
What's it do?
[TREYNI] Every Orc Lord
is born with this skill.
With the purpose of bringing
calamity and ruin to the world.
Its influence reaches all those
who serve under the Orc Lord.
Making them devour
everything in sight.
Doing so allows them to absorb
their victim's strength
and abilities.
Making those powers their own.
[ORCS] The strength of
this comrade we eat is now ours.
The abilities of this prey
are now ours.
[TREYNI] It's rather similar
to your Predator skill.
In return for the Starved skill,
they have an insatiable hunger.
The orcs march onward
with one goal in mind.
To sate an endless hunger
and gain power.
That is their king's, and their
whole clan's only wish.
[RIMURU sighs]
[RIMURU] So basically,
the orcs' goal isn't to wipe out
the superior forest races
like the lizardmen or the ogres.
What they want is to
steal their power. Right?
[RIMURU grunting]
Well, if that's really true,
sounds like we might need
to start worrying.
We have the Tempest Wolves,
Kijin and hobgoblins.
With those powers,
we might as well set the table
and invite the orcs
over for dinner.
I'm sure we'd make
a good side dish,
but aren't you forgetting
about the main course?
Huh?
[BENIMARU] We have the world's
strongest Slime, remember?
Oh, we do? [scoffs]
[chuckles]
[RIGURD]
Hmm!
What?
In addition,
we were recently able
to confirm that there is a majin
behind the Orc Lord's
sudden appearance.
I believe this is someone
you would not wish to overlook.
A majin.
This person is
a subordinate of a Demon Lord.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
[RIMURU] Treyni said
the dryads have knowledge
of everything that happens
in the forest.
She's very shrewd.
[sighs]
Rimuru Tempest.
Once again, I request
you defeat the Orc Lord.
As someone who has
the protection of Veldora,
has recruited the direwolves,
and became the patron
of the esteemed Kijin.
Taking down the Orc Lord
should be easy for you.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
What's your two cents,
Great Sage?
Can I trust the tree babe?
[GREAT SAGE]
The dryads are the caretakers
of the Great Forest of Jura.
They are said to be the ones
who pass divine justice
on villains
and any who would dare
to harm the forest.
[splat]
[RIMURU]
Sounds hardcore.
But 200,000 orcs is a lot.
Of course!
Lord Rimuru is quite capable
of vanquishing the Orc Lord.
I see.
Then you accept my request?
Yep.
[RIMURU] Shion! Don't I get
a say in this?
[SHION gasps]
[RIMURU] All right. I'll find
a way to defeat the Orc Lord.
But I'm gonna need
everyone here.
Sure. Count us in.
We'll help.
Yes, this is what
we've been waiting for.
We have complete faith
in your abilities,
just tell us what to do.
He's right, my lord.
Let's show those orcs
just how strong we are!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[TREYNI chuckles]
[RIMURU]
Sure, I talk a big game,
but what if we lose?
♪
If we're gonna take on
an army of 200,000 orcs,
then I think we should consider
forming an alliance
with the lizardmen after all.
But I'm not sure I wanna
talk to that guy again.
I am Gabiru!
[RIMURU]
Ugh!
I'd prefer to talk to someone
a little less stupid.
-[SOUEI] Lord Rimuru.
-[RIMURU] Huh?
Would you like for me
to go and speak
to the Lizardman Chieftain
personally?
-[RIMURU] Wow. Is that possible?
-Yes.
[RIMURU] The dude's brimming
with a cool confidence!
[gasps]
Uh, okay, then.
We'll join forces
with the lizardmen
and lay the hurt on some orcs!
[ALL]
Right!
[RIMURU] The battle
will probably take place
in the marshlands
where the lizardmen live.
Having their cooperation
will be essential
if we're going to pull this off.
I'm counting on you, Souei.
I'll leave now.
[RIMURU sighs]
[RIMURU] Hopefully their
Chieftain is less of an idiot.
The opposite of Gabiru.
[GABIRU groaning]
[LIZARDMAN crying]
Sir Gabiru!
[crying]
Oh, you're awake.
[LIZARDMAN]
Sir Gabiru!
Where... are we?
[LIZARDMAN crying]
Wait. I remember.
There was a fight.
And I was beaten
by that dopey-faced kid.
Hmm.
What a clever masquerade.
Huh? What do you mean?
[GABIRU]
It's simple, really.
The weird little hobgoblin
who beat me
is quite obviously
the true leader of that village!
♪
[ALL]
Really?
[LIZARDMAN 1]
That kid?
[LIZARDMAN 2]
He'd have to be
or there's no way
Sir Gabiru would have lost.
That's true.
[LIZARDMAN 2]
It's dirty.
They lied to make Sir Gabiru
lower his guard!
Those cowards.
-[LIZARDMAN 1] How dare they?!
-[GABIRU] Calm yourselves.
Only weaklings would
resort to such tricks.
[scoffs]
You're so wise.
Way to go, Sir Gabiru.
Truly amazing, sir.
That's our future Chieftain.
[LAPLACE] You're doing
a bang up job, Gabiru.
Oh, no. I'm really not
all that wonderful, guys.
Wait, who is that?!
He's been here the whole time.
[LAPLACE] You're just as
marvelous as all the rumors say.
The name's Laplace,
at your service.
[GABIRU]
Laplace?
[LAPLACE] Lord Gelmud has
sent me here on his behalf
to give you a teensy warning.
Warning? From Lord Gelmud?!
Uh, who's Lord Gelmud?
Don't you remember,
he's the person who gave
Sir Gabiru his name.
Thank you for coming
all the way out here.
Please, tell me about
this warning you speak of.
[LAPLACE] Well, we have
quite the crazy situation
on our hands.
It seems
that this army of orcs
is actually being led
by a big scawy monster
known as the Orc Lord.
[LIZARDMEN]
An actual Orc Lord?
[GABIRU grunts]
[LAPLACE]
Luckily the Lizardmen Chieftain
is very capable.
Though, he is getting up there
in his lizardy years.
I do wonder, can Daddy handle
such a massive challenge?
[GABIRU]
Hmm.
Originally, I had planned
on taking over as Chieftain
after we'd run off the orc army.
But it seems
that would be too late!
[LAPLACE]
Probably so.
♪
Excuse me.
I hate to rush off so suddenly,
but this is quite urge--
[LAPLACE] Say no more.
You're returning to
the marshlands, yes?
By all means, go.
Yes, thank you.
Let's get moving!
[LIZARDMEN]
Right!
♪
[LAPLACE] I'm sure
you'll do your best, Gabiru.
[ORCS] Trample all.
Trample all. Trample all.
Trample all.
♪
Chieftain, what are we
going to do?
The orc army's
quickly approaching.
There's not much we can do
except wait here.
We have no means
of fighting an army
200,000 strong.
-Right.
-[LIZARDMAN] Chieftain!
Sir, we have an intruder!
He's demanding to see you.
Right. Well, allow him inside.
But, Chieftain, it's not safe.
So you feel it too, it seems.
It's his aura.
I do.
He's no simple intruder.
He's strong.
I doubt even a hundred
of our best men
could stand against him.
[footsteps approaching]
♪
Forgive me.
We're presently
in a tough situation.
I can't spare much hospitality.
[SOUEI]
Don't trouble yourself.
I am only an envoy.
I come here today
bearing a message
from my lord and master.
[CHIEFTAIN]
Hmm.
[CHIEFTAIN] Very well.
What's the message?
An alliance.
My master wishes
to join forces with you.
[CHIEFTAIN]
An alliance? I see.
Unfortunately,
I have no real knowledge
concerning your master.
My master is known
as the Great Rimuru Tempest.
He recently received
a request from the dryads.
He has sworn that he will
defeat the orc army.
[gasps]
A request from
the Dryads? Truly?
She informed us
that this orc army
is being led by an Orc Lord.
Impossible!
[SOUEI] You may want to
keep that in mind
as you consider
our proposal.
[CHIEFTAIN grunting softly]
Yeah, right. Rimuru?
I've never heard of him.
This is all a ruse.
He probably sent you here
because he's afraid
of the Orc Lord.
He should admit his weakness
and just ask for our help.
-[CHIEFTAIN] Enough.
-Huh?
You need to hold your tongue.
But, sir, I cannot.
He's clearly here
to belittle our clan.
[groans]
[choking]
What is this?
[groaning]
Please, hold.
I apologize
for this one's rudeness.
And I ask that you forgive him.
I believe that your offer
would benefit us both equally.
[groaning]
[gasps]
[SOUEI]
Pardon me.
I did not come here
to make trouble.
But I won't let
my master be insulted.
[CHIEFTAIN]
Strong words.
Had I not stopped him, he would
have easily taken his head.
Judging by your aura,
you appear to be an ogre.
Are you from
the southwest region?
Was an ogre.
My master granted me
the name of "Souei"
and then I evolved into a Kijin.
What?
But isn't that the superior race
born only rarely from ogres?
[CHIEFTAIN]
If that's true,
it would mean that
your master is very powerful.
He must be of a race even more
superior than the Kijin.
An offer to enter an alliance.
And what's more, it comes right
on the heels of an Orc Lord
appearing in this world.
I would be foolish to refuse.
However...
Concerning this alliance,
I'll accept it on one condition.
[SOUEI]
Which is?
I wish to meet your master.
It was Rimuru Tempest, yes?
[SOUEI]
Very well.
Then we shall begin
preparations immediately.
We will meet you here
in seven days' time.
You can have an audience
with my master once he arrives.
[CHIEFTAIN]
Hmm.
You must ensure none of your men
engage in battle with the orcs
before we can get here.
[CHIEFTAIN]
I understand.
Thank you.
♪
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER]
Chieftain.
[CHIEFTAIN sighs]
Don't worry.
For there is light
at the end of this tunnel.
Gather everyone at once.
♪
Pay attention,
the orc army invasion
has already drawn
near to our lands
and this underground cave.
Stay calm.
We have nothing to fear.
In just seven days,
powerful reinforcements
will join us here.
Until then, we must
proceed with caution.
We need to conserve
our strength for this fight.
Under no circumstances are we
to make the first strike.
Those who fall in battle
will only be devoured
by the enemy
and enhance their strength.
Understood?
This is what it means to stand
against the legendary Orc Lord.
And once our reinforcements
join us,
we'll launch a counterattack.
You must resist
fighting until then.
I won't tolerate a single death
among my men.
[LIZARDMEN cheering]
[swords slashing]
[LIZARDMAN 1]
Good job. Surround him!
Was that monster
seriously an orc?
It was so strong it felt more
like we were fighting an ogre.
[LIZARDMAN 2]
It's hard to believe.
And just think,
there's 200,000 of these pigs.
[LIZARDMAN 1] That must be
the power of the Orc Lord.
We still have to defend
this place for three more days.
[GABIRU] If all we do is defend,
then we'll exhaust our strength.
[gasps]
It can't be.
-[GABIRU] Father.
-[CHIEFTAIN] Hmm?
Ah! You've returned.
Now then, tell me
all about your travels.
Were you able
to recruit any goblins?
Yes.
Seven thousand altogether.
I have them on standby.
Hmm.
But why are our forces in hiding
instead of preparing for battle?
The lizardmen are a proud race,
we should be fighting orcs,
not cowering in a cave.
Ah, while you were away
on your recruitment mission,
we were approached
with an offer of alliance.
Until our friends arrive
with reinforcements,
our best strategy
is to focus on defense.
[sighs]
You've aged, Father.
I've what?
[hisses]
♪
[gasps]
I agree utilizing
these natural labyrinths
may be a wise strategy
against a large army.
And yet, it also divides
our forces
between too many
separate corridors.
And stops us from meeting
our enemies at full strength.
Wait, Gabiru.
What's the meaning of all this?
Remain calm,
captain of the guard.
I have no intention
of harming you.
But...
[GABIRU]
I promise to apologize later
for resorting to violence.
And I hate to restrain you,
but bear with it until my men
and I defeat the Orc Lord.
Son, no.
Please, I beg you
not to do this.
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER]
Gabiru.
Brother, please!
This is madness!
[CHIEFTAIN]
Unhand me!
Let-let go at once!
You're making a mistake!
I won't stand for this!
Sir Gabiru, here.
That belongs to Father.
♪
Wait, this power...
Vortex Spear.
Does this mean you acknowledge
me as your master?
Sir, we've seized the leaders
of each clan per your request.
As it turns out,
a lot of the younger lizardmen
also did not agree
with these defensive tactics.
Good work.
We'll gladly follow your orders.
We're yours, Sir Gabiru.
Thank you. Now, get ready.
I'll show you how a true
lizardman fights.
The time has come!
[LIZARDMEN cheering]
[LIZARDMEN]
Gabiru! Gabiru!
Gabiru!
[ORCS]
Trample all. Trample all.
Trample all. Trample all...
[RIMURU] The orc army
soon enveloped the marshlands.
Then, from one corner
of their ranks, commotion arose.
[groaning]
[GABIRU]
There is no need to fear
these pigs any more than before.
These marshlands
are our domain!
We will throw the orcs
into confusion with our agility.
Those pigs are just big dimwits
whose feet will
get stuck in the mud!
All right!
[LIZARDMAN]
We're making a dent.
Sure are.
I told you these orcs
were no match for the lizardmen!
Right! Withdraw for now.
[RIMURU]
Gabiru's men had to acknowledge
his tactical talents.
[LIZARDMAN screaming]
[GABIRU]
What's happening?
[RIMURU] But there was one thing
they didn't account for.
Something Gabiru didn't know.
The Orc Lord's terror.
The orcs are eating
other orcs?
♪
[RIMURU]
Their Chieftain knew this.
About the Orc Lord's influence.
That gap in knowledge would have
consequences for Gabiru,
as he would soon see.
[ORCS]
Trample all.
Trample all. Trample all.
The strength of this comrade
we eat is now ours.
The abilities of this prey
are now ours!
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"The Great Clash."