[engines droning]
-[explosion]
-[clamoring, screaming]
[panicked chatter]
[WOMAN]
Come on, this way!
[screaming continues]
[panting]
Mommy! Mommy!
Where did you go?
Please, Mommy!
[gasps]
[overlapping chatter]
Sure is nice out today.
♪
My life is pretty normal
in the grand scheme of things.
I graduated from college
and landed a job
at a major contracting firm.
Then I worked my way
up the ladder, like you do,
and started making
some decent money.
I'm just your average
37-year-old man.
There is one thing missing.
I'm kind of lacking
in the girlfriend department.
By lacking, I mean I've never
had one at all, ever.
But to be perfectly honest,
it doesn't bother me that much.
Satoru! Hey, there.
Good to see you.
Tamura. Hey. Sorry, I'm late.
What was it you needed?
Hi, I'm Miho,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
I've seen you around
the office before,
but I don't think
we've ever been introduced.
Ah. Of course.
I'm Satoru Mikami.
Come to think of it,
I've actually heard
a lot about you.
Huh? Wait. You have?
Yeah. I mean,
there's plenty of rumors.
[gasps]
Uh, what kind of rumors?
Miho. Calm down, he's kidding.
Go easy on her, she's not
used to your jokes yet.
Sure, sorry.
Why am I even here?
Does he want marriage advice
or something?
Do you wanna grab some food?
We can talk over dinner.
You said that
you like yakiniku, right?
Come on, I know
the perfect place.
[SATORU]
Yeesh.
He made plans revolving around
my favorite food?
He's really buttering me up.
It's right up here.
[SATORU] They're good kids.
I should congratulate them.
[WOMAN screaming]
[panting]
[gasps]
[gasping]
Tamura!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[onlookers scream]
[overlapping chatter]
[groaning]
Satoru!
[gasping]
[SATORU]
Hey, what's going on?
This heat, I can't stand it.
It's too hot.
[FEMALE VOICE]
Request confirmed.
Acquisition of the skill
"Heat Resistance" is successful.
[SATORU] Is this it?
Death by stabbing?
What the hell?
[VOICE]
Request confirmed.
Acquisition of the skill
Stab Resistance is successful.
Continuing.
Physical Attack Resistance.
Acquisition Successful.
Send an ambulance! Hurry!
[SATORU]
There's so much blood. It hurts.
[VOICE] Request confirmed.
Pain Nullification acquired.
Creating a body
that does not require blood.
Successful.
[SATORU] Calm down.
You've gotta man up, Tamura.
[gasping]
Satoru! Hang on!
[SATORU]
And now I'm cold.
[VOICE]
Cold Resistance Acquisition.
Successful.
Attainment of both
Heat Resistance
and Cold Resistance
has resulted in a new skill:
Thermal Fluctuation Resistance.
[SATORU]
Am I going to die?
Hey, Tamura.
[shudders]
Promise me something.
My computer's hard drive,
I need you to, to dump it
in the bathtub and fry it.
[TAMURA]
Huh?
[VOICE] Deletion of data
via electronic current
has failed due to
insufficient information.
As an alternative,
Electric Current Resistance
has been acquired.
Paralysis Resistance
is included.
Successful.
Satoru.
Tamura.
Listen.
The reason I wanted
to have dinner
was so I could show off Miho
like a total jerk.
Yeah. I know.
Don't worry about it.
Mister Mikami.
Just promise me, you'll have
a happy life together.
And please,
wipe my hard drive.
[shuddering]
[SATORU] I can't believe
I'm gonna kick the bucket
as a girlfriend-less virgin.
In my next life
I'm gonna go on the prowl.
I'll hunt down all the ladies.
[VOICE]
Acquisition of Unique Skill:
Predator. Successful.
[SATORU] In stories,
30-year-old virgins are wizards.
Seeing as I'm pushing 40,
guess that makes me
some kind of sage.
A few more years
and I'd be a great sage.
[VOICE]
Extra Skill Acquired: Sage.
Continuing, Sage will transform
into the Unique Skill:
Great Sage. Successful.
[SATORU]
Shut up already.
Can't a guy...
just get some peace and quiet?
[gasps]
[TAMURA]
Satoru?
Satoru!
[SATORU]
It's so dark. I can't see.
Where the heck am I?
And what happened to me?
The last thing I remember
is someone teasing me
about being a sage or whatever.
Hold on.
I was stabbed.
Yeah, okay, then.
It'll be all right.
No need to panic just yet.
I mean, I haven't lost
my cool in a while.
The last time was when I crapped
my pants back in grade school.
Anyway, back to
the stabbing thing.
Let's see.
I don't hurt anywhere.
I'm not cold.
But my eyes, they won't open.
I can't see anything.
My hands, my feet.
I can't feel them.
My body...
[sighs]
I can move!
At least there's that.
Are those rocks?
Which would mean
I'm not in the hospital.
Okay, so where the hell am I?
Huh?
What's this? Some kinda plant?
Does my mouth work? Can I talk?
Nope. Whoa!
It dissolved!
No way!
I think I can feel it permeating
throughout my whole body.
Hold up.
That doesn't seem normal.
What happened to me?
My body's never been able
to dissolve plants before.
Right?
Wait.
Huh? Huh?
Maybe I really did kick it.
I wonder what happened
to Tamura and Miho.
[echoing] He better have fried
my hard drive!
Still though,
what the heck am I?
I feel kind of bouncy
and rubbery.
It seems like my whole body
is that way.
Uh-huh.
I think I get it.
Is this really possible?
Can it be that my totally real
and not made-up,
hot and muscular dude-bod
has now been streamlined
into this small gelatinous form?
Yeah, right! There's no way
I'd be that chill about it!
But I can't deny it either.
[sighs]
Human I am not.
No doubt.
It appears I was stabbed, died,
and reincarnated as a slime.
I'm pretty sure a lot of time
has passed since my rebirth.
All things considered,
the slime body thing
isn't such a bad deal.
And it comes with the weird perk
of not needing sleep or food.
So, what's the point
of eating these plants, you ask?
Because I'm so freakin' bored!
There's no real point to it
but it's better than
doing nothing.
Wait. Who am I even talking to?
Maybe the bigger question
is where does the stuff
I eat even go?
It's not like I poop.
-[VOICE] Answer.
-[screams]
The plants are stored
in the stomach
of your Unique Skill: Predator.
[SATORU]
Whoa, a voice?
It sounds like the one I heard
when I was shanked.
Who are you?
[VOICE]
Answer.
It is the effect of
your Unique Skill: Great Sage.
Now that your ability
has been established,
you will be capable
of reacting more quickly.
[SATORU]
"Great Sage"?
So when you say skill,
do you mean like, my abilities?
What is "Predator"?
[GREAT SAGE]
It allows you to ingest objects
and analyze them
within your body.
You can then acquire
that object's skills.
Once the analysis is complete,
you can then mimic the object.
[SATORU]
Oh!
[GREAT SAGE] The stomach stores
the objects you ingest.
Additionally, it can also
isolate harmful objects
that cannot be analyzed.
[SATORU]
Uh, I'm not gonna lie,
the Predator skill
sounds kinda amazing.
Is it really something
a slime should possess?
Not that I'm complaining.
Hey, as a test can you analyze
that plant I just ate?
Confirmed, analysis complete.
It is a Hipokute herb.
A valuable herb that only grows
in areas rich in magicules.
Used as an ingredient
in salves and healing potions.
-Magicules?
-Magicules.
A special energetic material
found in all--
[SATORU] Argh! Can't you
use simpler words?
[GREAT SAGE] Magicules are
the building blocks of life
in all magical beings.
[SATORU] Building blocks, eh?
Makes sense.
I bet this cave is
full of those magicule thingies.
Which is probably why
this place is Hipokute heaven!
So, basically since
I just ate all those plants.
I can analyze them
in my stomach.
Does that mean I can create
like healing potions
and then stash them away
for a rainy day
inside my slime
storage locker?
-[dinging]
-[GREAT SAGE] Affirmative.
[SATORU]
Awesome sauce! Right!
Off I went,
gobbling up Hipokute herbs
like they were
going out of style.
Then I analyzed those babies
and turned them into
some juicy healing potions
via slime stomach.
I figured they might
come in handy.
But once again,
I was mostly just doing it
to fight off my boredom.
[sighs]
You know, I thought
all those plants
were pretty darn worthless
until I actually analyzed them.
Hey, Great Sage,
what's the deal with this rock?
[GREAT SAGE]
Magistone ore.
Minerals that spend
long periods of time
in magicule-rich areas
take in magicules
until they become magistone ore.
It's considered valuable.
Whoa, for real? All righty!
[SATORU] Man, I've really hit
the jackpot in here.
♪
I devoured every magistone ore
I could find.
Which was a lot!
It was like an ore smorgasbord!
[grunts]
[screams, groaning]
Oh, man. This feels weird.
Did I just fall in water?
Like, in a lake?
I guess slimes don't float.
Ah, crap, am I gonna die again?
I can still breathe though.
Or not breathe, wait, could I
even breathe to start with?
Probably not.
Anyway, what am I gonna do?
I can't swim.
That's it!
I'll just suck in
a bunch of water.
[grunts]
Okay!
[GREAT SAGE] Skill: Water
Pressure Propulsion acquired.
[yelling]
Wait. I don't have any brakes!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[groans]
I'm almost positive
there's a dent in my head,
but why doesn't it hurt?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
Because you have
the Pain Nullification skill,
you do not feel pain.
The amount of damage
you've sustained is ten percent.
Species skill Self-Regeneration
has been activated.
[SATORU]
So, I can still take damage
even though I don't feel pain?
[gasps]
[grunts]
Whoa, my body just buffed
out its own dent.
Score! Now that's
a convenient skill!
Still though,
I should probably
be more careful
from here on out.
-[MALE VOICE] You there.
-[gasps]
Can you hear me, small one?
I said, "Can you hear me,
small one?"
-[whimpers]
-Hey!
It's rude to just ignore me.
[SATORU]
Uh, are they talking to me?
[MALE VOICE]
You had best answer me.
[SATORU]
Easier said than done!
I don't have a mouth
to talk with, genius.
-Hey!
Stop shouting, baldy!
Oh-ho-ho.
You dare to call me "baldy"?
You're rather bold for a slime.
Unh.
[roaring]
[screaming]
I was trying to be hospitable
seeing it's been a while
since my last visitor.
But perhaps you have
a death wish!
[SATORU]
Hey, man, I'm really sorry!
I didn't know you could
read my mind or whatever!
And I don't have
eyes or a mouth
so I'm literally
in the dark here.
[evil laughter]
[gasps]
I thought you were brave to
call me baldy after seeing me,
but it turns out
you are blind.
Fine. I shall
bestow sight upon you.
Huh?
However, there are
a few small conditions.
What say you?
[SATORU]
Uh, depends on the conditions.
[MALE VOICE]
They're fairly simple.
You must promise not to fear me
when you gain
the ability to see.
And I'd like for you to come
and visit again sometime.
That is all. Are those
terms agreeable to you?
Wait, is that seriously it?
Yes. You see, small one,
I was sealed in this cave
300 years ago.
Ever since then,
I've had nothing to do
other than be
exceptionally bored.
So, do we have a deal?
[SATORU] Well, I'm kinda curious
about the whole sealed thing,
but, whatever,
you got a deal!
Excellent.
There is a skill
called Magic Sense.
Can you use it?
I don't know what it is.
It allows you to sense
the magicules around you.
So if I can detect those
magicules, I'd be able to see?
All right, I'll give it a shot.
[grunting in effort]
Hey, something's happening!
Is this what magicules
look like?
Oh! [chuckles]
[GREAT SAGE] Extra skill:
Magic Sense acquired.
[SATORU]
Oh snap! Wait, "extra skill"?
Skills with power
and efficiency
which are higher
than those of normal skills.
Whoa! That sounds
extra awesome!
[GREAT SAGE] Would you like
to use Magic Sense?
[SATORU]
Yes!
Whoa! [chuckles]
I can see! I can see!
I can see, see, see!
Oh, yeah!
Bummer alert.
I really am a slime.
-[MALE VOICE] How'd it go?
-[SATORU] Great.
I did it! Thank you so much.
[groans, screams]
Holy crap! You're a dragon?!
[groaning]
Allow me to formally
introduce myself.
Uh, sure.
I am Veldora.
The Storm Dragon.
That sounds serious.
I am one of only four
True Dragons
that exist in this world.
[evil laughter]
Hey, don't forget
our deal, slime.
I would never!
It's not like I'm scared!
But I gotta run, so I'll come
and visit sometime. Bye!
-Hold it!
-[squeals]
Something is amiss.
Slimes are normally low-ranked
monsters that do not think.
Yet you seem intelligent.
Are you Unique?
I honestly don't know
what that means.
It refers to a being
with extraordinary abilities.
[SATORU]
I may be. I don't know.
The truth is,
I used to be a human.
Then I got stabbed
to death and sha-bam.
The next thing I knew
I looked like this.
[VELDORA] Yes, I see.
You were reincarnated.
[SATORU]
I guess.
And now I'm living my life
as a slime monster.
[VELDORA]
It is very unusual
for someone to come
into this world that way.
Huh? It is?
Occasionally,
there are others
who will come here
from a different world.
But you are the first I've known
that was reincarnated here.
Most beings are unable
to withstand
having only their soul
traverse worlds.
[SATORU] Wait, so there are
people who come here
from other worlds,
but never through reincarnation?
Hmm. We call them
"Otherworlders."
I've heard that they gain
special abilities
based on their desires
when they cross into this land.
Oh, that makes sense.
That's probably
how I got my skills.
I wonder if there are
other people from Japan here.
I think I'm gonna go try
and find some of
those Otherworlders.
[VELDORA] What's this?
You're leaving so soon?
[SATORU]
The dude's pouting?
Well, uh...
I guess I could stay
a little longer.
I mean, there's no rush
or anything.
Excellent!
Please stay as long as you like!
[SATORU sighs]
Oh, yeah, didn't you mention
something earlier
about how you were sealed
in this cave, Veldora?
Yes, it's a great story.
It was 300 years ago.
I sort of accidentally
burned down an entire town.
[SATORU]
"Accidentally"?
[VELDORA] So of course,
someone came looking to slay me.
It's possible
that I underestimated
my opponent a bit.
About halfway through the battle
I started using
my full strength.
Yet I still lost somehow!
Seriously?
But you seem like
a pretty strong dude.
Was your opponent
super powerful?
Yes, extremely powerful.
The humans called her a hero,
blessed with divine protection.
[SATORU]
A blessed hero?
Sounds like something
out of a video game.
[VELDORA]
Using her Unique Skill,
she overpowered me in battle.
And then sealed me away
using Unlimited Imprisonment.
[SATORU]
Is that shiny stuff
her Unlimited
Imprisonment spell?
Yes.
Also, you should know
the hero referred to herself
as something called
a "Summon."
A Summon?
Is that supposed to be
different from an Otherworlder?
It requires more than
30 mages performing a ritual
that lasts several days
to bring someone here.
Sweet! You guys have mages here?
This is starting to sound
more like a game!
The Summon is expected
to perform as a powerful weapon.
[SATORU]
A weapon?
[VELDORA]
Yes, for the Summoner.
They use magic to carve a curse
into the Summon's soul.
That way they can
never defy their master.
What the heck?
That's seriously messed up, man!
Is it?
I'm not sure
what your world was like,
but in this world,
the only thing that matters
is survival of the fittest.
[SATORU]
Huh.
So, you've been
stuck in this cave
ever since that hero sealed you
here 300 years ago?
That is correct.
I am so incredibly bored.
Man, and here I thought
I was lonely
just because I never had
a girlfriend
in my previous life.
Being all alone for 300 years
would be a real suck fest.
That's it!
Hey, what if you
and I became friends?
Are you serious?
Me, the mighty
Storm Dragon, Veldora,
become friends
with a lowly slime?!
Yeah, you're right.
It was a stupid idea.
Now, hold on.
I never said
that I didn't want to.
So, uh, does that mean
you're cool with it?
I suppose
I could make an exception.
Just this once,
I'd be willing to consider it.
[SATORU]
Playing hard to get?
Fine, that settles it, then.
We're friends.
Unless of course you'd rather
hang out here alone.
No, I wouldn't.
Today is your lucky day, slime!
We'll be friends.
Whatever makes you
feel better about it.
Well, put her there, pal!
Right. Pal.
[SATORU]
It's kind of weird
trying to make
new friends at my age,
-and with a dragon, no less.
-[VELDORA laughs]
[SATORU]
Anyway, that's the story
of how I got stabbed, died,
was reincarnated as a slime,
and made friends
with the super powerful
Storm Dragon, Veldora.
My totally normal life
as a 37-year-old man
is ancient history.
I still can't believe
all that's happened.
But this is my new life now.
Or should I call it a "slife"?
Oh, yeah.
I hope Tamura remembered
to wipe my hard drive for me.
Man, I hope he didn't look
to see what's on it.
[grunting]
[crackles]
[hissing]
All done.
Please rest in peace, Satoru.
If I ever have a son,
I'll name him after the hero
who saved my life.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
“Meeting the Goblins.”