Stupid jerk!
That was
my bestie's subordinate!
[grunting]
[PHOBIO]
Damn it! She'll pay for that.
She should know
who she's messing with.
I'm Phobio,
the Black Leopard Fang.
There's not much we can
possibly do
with Demon Lord Milim
in the picture.
Even if Demon Lord Carrion
does command it.
Shut up!
Demon Lord Carrion wouldn't have
got his ass kicked like a loser.
The hard truth is
that I just wasn't good enough.
And my pride won't let me
go back empty-handed.
So now I don't know what to do.
You saw it.
Those guys built a thriving town
all on their own.
I treated them as if they were
just lowly monsters,
but they have skills
and techniques
that even we lack.
It's true.
Instead of ordering them
to serve us,
I would have liked to have tried
and establish
diplomatic relations with them.
Agreed.
Even if Lady Milim
hadn't stepped in,
I still handled that thing
all wrong.
I'll never gain their trust.
Not when I tried to take over
without giving them a say.
Not that it matters now.
My wounds may have healed,
but I'll never recover
from that humiliation.
I have to find a way
to get revenge on her somehow,
that way I don't cause
any more trouble
for Lord Carrion.
Sure, all that's easy to say,
but it's not exactly realistic.
I already know!
I don't need your stupid advice.
Lookit, I'm just really
frustrated right now.
[grunting]
[MAN guffawing]
Who goes there?
♪
[CLOWN]
I do understand how you feel.
It must be very frustrating
to be so utterly frustrated.
Greetings, fine people.
I'm Footman, and it's a pleasure
to meet you.
Footman?
[FOOTMAN]
I'm a member of the esteemed
Moderate Harlequin Alliance,
the one known as
Footman, the Angry Pierrot.
Please hold your applause.
[PHOBIO groans]
[TEAR] There's no need for
all those suspicious groans.
I'm Tear.
Don't worry,
we're friendly clowns.
[FOOTMAN]
Mm-hmm.
What do you want?
[FOOTMAN laughs]
[FOOTMAN]
If you must know,
I was summoned here
by all the angry
and hateful vibes
you're giving off.
[PHOBIO]
What's that supposed to mean?
[FOOTMAN]
I'm saying I was drawn here
by your feelings of rage.
[PHOBIO gasps]
[FOOTMAN] Why don't you tell me
what has angered you so?
I'd love to hear it.
I'm quite certain I could be
of assistance to you.
[PHOBIO exhales]
Ignore them.
You don't have to answer
to these ridiculous clowns,
Sir Phobio.
Would you like me
to dispose of them?
We are the Beastketeers
who proudly serve
under Demon Lord Carrion.
A couple of wandering majin
like yourselves
are no match for us.
[FOOTMAN]
You desire power, do you not?
We have that in spades.
More than
you've ever seen before.
However, it comes
with great risk.
Should you not be scared
by that teensy little detail.
The power you stand to gain
is unfathomable.
Really?
My Lord.
[TEAR] If you wanna defeat
that mean ol' Demon Lord Milim,
then all you gotta do is become
a real Demon Lord yourself.
[gasps]
What?
Seriously?
Do you actually think
you can fool me
with that kind of nonsense?
-[FOOTMAN] Charybdis.
-[PHOBIO gasps]
♪
[FOOTMAN]
Does it ring any bells?
The Charybdis?
Really?
[ENRIO gasps]
[TEAR]
Uh-huh.
If you could harness the power
of the giant whale fish thing,
then you'd be as powerful
as the Demon Lord.
But if you're not interested,
we can always find someone else.
Let's go, Footman.
[FOOTMAN]
Mm-hmm-hmm.
What a shame.
Hold on.
[BOTH]
Hmm?
Don't do this. It's madness.
[PHOBIO] Listen, I haven't liked
any of this from the start.
Like, why did a fat, useless orc
get chosen to be
the next Demon Lord?
It's not fair!
If they needed
a new Demon Lord,
then why didn't
they choose me?!
But if I were to get stronger,
even Lord Carrion would have
no choice but to forgive me.
Sir Phobio.
I want to know more.
[FOOTMAN] Ah.
A very wise move, Sir Phobio.
Not that I'm surprised.
It's obvious you possess
the talents
to become a Demon Lord.
[TEAR] It's not fair
that someone weaker than you
got a shot at being
a Demon Lord first.
I'm with you on that.
Especially when you're
the best person for the job.
[ENRIO]
Hmm.
So tell me,
what do you stand to gain
from all this?
What are you after?
[TEAR] Oh, we just want
special treatment
once you become a Demon Lord.
And, you know, maybe you could
do us a couple of small favors.
[FOOTMAN laughs]
Besides, it's not
as if we're capable
of subduing Charybdis
on our own.
[TEAR]
We did happen to find the place
where it's sealed away,
but without help, we're just
sitting on a gold mine.
[FOOTMAN] But then
we happened to find you,
so perfect timing, right?
Yeah, maybe.
Still though, we don't even know
if I'll have the ability
to control Charybdis
in the first place.
[FOOTMAN]
Ho-ho-ho.
Don't be so modest,
if anyone can do it, you can!
[TEAR]
You'll be fantastic.
[PHOBIO]
So in exchange for their help,
all they want are a few favors
and the credit
for helping me reach the top?
All right, then.
I accept your offer.
♪
[PHOBIO]
Go back without me.
Don't do this.
Report on everything
that has happened.
But, sir...
I cannot cause more trouble
for Lord Carrion.
So tell him that I'm resigning.
I'm no longer a part
of the Beastketeers.
Thank you for everything
you've done, Enrio.
[ENRIO]
Sir Phobio.
I will become stronger.
Then Demon Lord Milim
will suffer
under the wrath of my power.
[ENRIO gasps]
As you wish.
I'll report to Lord Carrion.
I warn you, the extent of
Charybdis' power is unknown.
So please be careful, sir.
♪
[ENRIO] Sir Phobio is a not
a foolish man.
If what they say is true,
and Charybdis does exist,
I'm certain he'll find a way
to control it.
[FOOTMAN]
Come. We have much to do.
Yeah.
The sooner I can combine
my power with Charybdis,
the sooner I can make
Demon Lord Milim pay.
I'll wipe that smug look
off her face.
[FOOTMAN laughs]
That's the spirit.
[TEAR] Uh-huh.
We'll be cheerin' for ya.
[indistinct chatter]
[ALL gasp]
There, you see?
I told you I'd win.
Looks like I'm the
stay-under-water
breath-holding champion.
Sorry, but I was
the winner here.
You were?
But I was the last one up.
By a few seconds.
You guys are acting
like sore losers.
Shion. Shuna.
Okay. We'll do another round.
Let's settle the score.
Very well.
It's on.
It's not a good idea to stay
underwater in the bath,
but one more time
shouldn't hurt.
[ALL]
Ready?
[ALL inhale]
[RIMURU] Aw.
Sounds like they're having fun.
Kinda wish I had bathed
on that side.
Over here there's just...
an old dude.
Hey, how long are you planning
on hanging around?
Do you still think
we're like evil or whatever?
Huh? No, I don't.
To be completely honest,
I stopped being suspicious
of you guys a while back.
[RIMURU]
Then why haven't you left?
Because this town you've built
is pretty relaxing,
all things considered.
I can't remember the last time
I took a break.
So I thought I'd take this
opportunity to slow down a bit.
[RIMURU]
Seriously?
What happened to the whole
"I will see for myself
whether or not you're truly
an ally of humans" spiel?
For a second there,
you sounded pretty cool.
[FUZE sighs]
[RIMURU]
He's not even listening?!
-Hey!
-[FUZE] Hmm?
[RIMURU] What's the status on
Youm and his group?
You promised to help us
make them look like champions,
or is that part
of your brain on break, too?
Ha, ha.
[RIMURU]
"Ha, ha" isn't answer!
I bet you don't even know
they left.
They rode off to build
their reputation,
lookin' fly as hell.
You really should relax
a little bit.
Besides, I've already finished
setting things up.
[RIMURU]
You have?
[FUZE]
Yes.
Believe it or not, I've already
done the ground work
for spreading the rumors
that they're the champions
who defeated the Orc Lord.
Of course, I was sure
to include all the details.
Like how you and your people
are nothing,
but a friendly town of monsters
who gave them supplies
for their quest.
[RIMURU]
Oh.
Awesome sauce.
It looks like he's slacking off,
but he's actually ahead
of the game.
[FUZE] Well, I think
I've soaked enough.
[RIMURU]
Before I forget,
I wanted to mention that
I'm thinking of building a road
from our town
to the Kingdom of Blumund.
[gasps]
Wait. What? Seriously?
Uh, look,
I think it's a fine idea.
But we're talking about
a national undertaking here.
Think of how much it would cost.
[RIMURU]
Chill out, Fuze, my boy.
"Your boy?"
Having you call me
that sounds weird.
I mean, I'm not even sure
how old you really are.
[RIMURU]
Meh, details schmetails.
Having a road would make it
easier for us to do business.
My people can handle paving it
and all the physical work.
However...
However?
[RIMURU] I'd like to sell
some of our specially made goods
to other countries.
So, I was hoping
that you could introduce me
to someone who can
give me some advice.
Is that all?
That sounds simple enough.
[RIMURU]
Sweetness.
[GIRLS giggling]
-[RIMURU] Huh?
-[excited chatter]
[RIMURU] I definitely
should have gone to that side.
♪
It's in here?
[TEAR]
Sure is.
[FOOTMAN]
It hasn't been revived yet,
but can't you feel its thirst
for destruction pouring out?
Such emotions make for
the most tantalizing treats.
Hence how we were able
to find it.
Yeah, you're right.
There's an ominous feeling
in the air.
Charybdis.
[FOOTMAN]
Under normal circumstances,
reviving Charybdis
would require many corpses.
Corpses?
[FOOTMAN] Right, you see
it's really more of
a spiritual life form.
In order to utilize its power
in this world,
someone has to provide it
with a physical body to inhabit.
I get that. So what?
You haven't realized
your role yet?
Hold on.
You mean...
[FOOTMAN]
When we say "subdue,"
what we really mean
is you have to take
Charybdis into your body.
Then you'll merge together
into one all-powerful being!
Are you serious?
[TEAR]
It's not too late to turn back.
-But...
-Spit it out.
[TEAR] I'm not sure the seal
can hold out for much longer.
And if it doesn't? Then what?
[TEAR] It would find a way
to revive on its own, I guess.
[PHOBIO] But you just said
it needs corpses.
[TEAR]
Yes, true!
But I'm sure
it's more than capable
of acquiring the corpses
it needs
for revival all by itself,
with or without our help.
And in that case,
us and everyone around us
will be doomed.
[FOOTMAN]
How right you are.
[TEAR] If it manages
to revive on its own,
it'll be uncontrollable.
And since it won't have
a living vessel to guide it,
then it will surely
do whatever it wants.
[PHOBIO] So you're saying
we need to break the seal
and take its power
before it can wake up?
[TEAR]
Huh? Well, yeah.
That should do the trick.
[FOOTMAN]
Very perceptive.
Fine then.
I'm going to break the seal
and make its power my own.
[footsteps]
Charybdis.
I'll do it.
I'll subdue it with my own body.
And then I'll get my revenge
on Demon Lord Milim.
[FOOTMAN]
He actually went in.
[TEAR]
He sure did.
[FOOTMAN] That's a minion
of Lord Carrion for you,
all muscle and no brain.
[TEAR]
Makes things easier for us.
[BOTH cackling]
[FOOTMAN] Does that mean
the task is finished?
[TEAR]
I think so.
All Lord Clayman told me
was to revive Charybdis
and send it towards Milim.
-Hey.
-[FOOTMAN] Ooh?
[TEAR] I left Lesser Dragon
corpses here earlier,
but now they've disappeared.
[FOOTMAN] Oh, well, so long
as we're prepared,
there's nothing to worry about.
[BOTH cackling]
[groans]
It's so heavy.
[laughing]
Pretty impressive haul, huh?
[RIMURU]
Uh-huh.
Lady Milim is just amazing.
She's able to locate monsters
right away.
It actually makes hunting them
pretty easy.
[MILIM laughs]
Finding monsters is simple
when you're amazing.
We're gonna feast again tonight.
[RIMURU]
Good job.
Excellent work, everyone.
Work's definitely a way
to describe it.
Who wants to get a drink
and a bath?
I'd love a drink.
[laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
-[SHION] Lady Milim.
-[MILIM gasps]
Who goes there?
-[MILIM] Hmph.
-[RIMURU] Careful!
Whoa, I've got you.
[RIMURU]
This presence!
♪
[RIMURU]
It's Treyni.
No, wait, she seems different.
Huh? It's a dryad!
Well, this is a first.
Hello, there.
I am the Dryad Trya.
Treyni's younger sister.
[RIMURU]
Treyni's little sis?!
Uh, wait, what's up
with the ominous aura
you're emanating?
An emergency has arisen.
Calamity approaches us all.
[RIMURU]
Like, how so?
A calamity-class monster
Charybdis has been revived.
[RIMURU]
Charyb-what?
[TRYA] Its violence equals
that of a Demon Lord.
My sisters, including Treyni,
have set out
to slow its progress,
but they aren't
strong enough.
There's more.
Judging by the monster's path,
it's heading for this town.
[ALL gasp]
Against Charybdis, who's known
as the Ruler of the Skies,
waging a war on land is futile.
I've come to warn you
about your defenses.
Form an airborne combat force.
There isn't much time left.
[TRYA]
The monster known as Charybdis
was born a long time ago.
And has died
and been revived many times.
It is the violent
Ruler of the Skies.
However, based on its lineage,
that's to be expected.
It hails from Veldora,
the guardian of the forest.
[RIMURU]
Like it's Veldora's child?
[TRYA]
Yes, in a way.
You see Charybdis was generated
from a cloud
of Veldora's magicules.
[RIMURU] So does that mean
the fish thing and I
are kind of like siblings?
Wait.
I wonder if that's why
it's heading to our village.
Maybe it knows that I've got
Veldora stashed in my stomach.
If Charybdis has truly revived,
then it's far more dangerous
than a Demon Lord.
Because unlike most enemies,
we have no way of speaking
with this opponent.
True, it's a monster
with zero intelligence.
It's said to have the ability to
summon floating shark creatures,
known as Megalodons, who then
come from the spirit world
to join it in its rampage.
So I've heard, anyway.
[RIMURU]
Man, for real?
And I thought the Orc Lord
was bad.
To make things even worse,
the Megalodons
that it's summoned,
well, it looks like
they've possessed
some Lesser Dragon corpses
that happened to be nearby.
[RIMURU]
What?
[TRYA]
There are 13 of them.
[RIMURU] Great, so there's
a fish as strong as Demon Lord,
and 13 shark lackeys
following it.
Easy-peasy lemon squeezy.
Lord Rimuru,
what should we do?
[RIMURU]
I'm not sure yet.
-[MILIM snickers]
-[RIMURU] Huh?
Come on, are you sure you're not
forgetting someone important?
That stupid fish...
is no match for a Demon Lord.
I'll obliterate Charybdis.
[RIMURU] Hell, yeah!
Why didn't I think of that?
I'm sorry, but we can't
allow you to.
[MILIM gasps]
This is our town,
and therefore our problem.
[RIMURU] But it doesn't
have to be just our problem!
Huh? Really?
But I'm his bestie.
Shion's right.
We can't rely on you
for everything
just because
you're our friend.
When Lord Rimuru is in
desperate need of help,
when he's out of options,
we'll call on you, Lady Milim.
[RIMURU]
I'm feeling pretty desperate
right now, though.
-[RIMURU chuckles nervously]
-[MILIM groaning]
[RIMURU]
They're right, Milim.
Just have faith in me.
[groans]
But I... I thought...
I'd finally get my chance
to shine a little, you know?
[RIMURU]
I guess Charybdis is after me.
So it's not fair
to rely on Milim.
-[MILIM groaning]
-[RIMURU] Hmm!
Begin preparations
to defeat Charybdis.
[ALL]
Right.
[MILIM]
This whole thing is so unfair.
Beat Charybdis?
Listen, this won't be easy.
Not even the dryads
can take this monster down.
You know that, right?
[RIMURU]
Thanks to the treaty,
we can count on King Gazel
for back up.
We'll just have to do our best.
Why not just run away?
[RIMURU]
What good would that do?
Look, I'm the strongest guy
in this nation.
If things start to look
really bad,
then I'll bail
and think up a new plan.
But in the meantime, I should
at least face this thing head-on
and see how
strong it is, right?
Yes, perhaps.
I mean, you are the leader.
It makes sense.
[RIMURU]
We're different from humans,
you guys are done for
if something happens
to your king.
[FUZE]
Well, that may be the case,
but one thing I've noticed
about you these past few days
is that you reason
much like a human.
It's kind of hard to think
of you as a monster.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
You may be on to something.
This might be tough to believe,
but once upon a time,
I actually used
to be a human.
You know about Shizu, right?
I'm pretty sure
I'm an otherworlder,
just like she was.
I died in my world.
And then, I was reincarnated
here as a slime.
[FUZE gasping]
You're like Shizu?
She and I are
from the same place.
That's why she entrusted
everything to me.
I gained this human form
in exchange
for inheriting her will.
And I can't exactly go around
making dumb mistakes
while I look like Shizu.
I see.
As far as I'm concerned,
that makes you someone
we can trust.
[FUZE]
Hmm.
Besides, I made
a promise to Shizu.
About what?
That I'd clear away the feelings
that bind her heart.
That's what I promised.
So my prey is Demon Lord Leon.
Whoa, seriously?
Yeah. What he said.
It takes a lot of guts
to call a guy
like Demon Lord Leon your prey.
I mean, if you have to
fight one of the two,
then I guess Charybdis
is probably
easier to handle, right?
Agreed.
The Demon Lord can wait.
Charybdis comes first.
[RIMURU]
The land between
the Jura Tempest
Federation's capital city
and the armed nation of Dwargon
was about to become
a battlefield.
The allied forces
were in the path
of an immensely
powerful opponent.
Its name?
♪
The calamity-class Charybdis.
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time, "Charybdis."