[RIMURU]
It's been a couple of days
since the Kijin
joined our squad.
[GARM]
Ho-ho-ho.
Now this is some quality stuff.
Uh-huh.
So you're saying this fabric
is basically silk, Shuna?
-Really?
-That's right.
See, it's actually made
from hellmoth cocoons.
Those things are
full of magicules,
which makes the cloth durable.
Oh, I see. It should be useful
for protective gear, then.
-[RIMURU] That's so cool!
-[ALL gasp]
I can't believe
you guys can already weave silk.
[SHUNA]
Lord Rimuru.
-Hello.
-Hey, there.
[MYRD]
Hmm.
[RIMURU]
Will you just say something?!
[SHUNA]
I'm so happy you came to visit.
Come here, you.
[RIMURU]
Uh, no problem.
-How are things going?
-Great.
The weaving loom that Sir Kaijin
made for me is perfect,
and it's so easy to use.
[RIMURU]
Yeah? That's good to hear!
I'm counting on you to help
make us all clothes, okay?
You got it.
Just leave it to me.
Well, we should probably go,
Lord Rimuru.
We don't want your lunch
to get cold.
Oh, Shion.
Are you enjoying your new job
as our lord's secretary?
Yes, as a matter of fact I am.
[RIMURU] Shion went and declared
herself my secretary.
She kinda looked the part
so I just rolled with it.
On top of all that,
she's also my new bodyguard.
[SHUNA giggles]
You know, Shion, you could
always leave Lord Rimuru
here with me for a bit.
Oh, princess. We don't want
to get in your way.
After all, you still have
lots of clothes to make.
[RIMURU]
It's only a hunch,
but I think there's
some tension here.
[SHUNA]
No worries.
Believe it or not, I'm actually
very good at multitasking.
[SHION] We wouldn't want him
to miss out on lunch, though.
♪
In that case,
I suppose we'll just
have to ask Lord Rimuru
which one of us he would prefer
to serve him, won't we?
[RIMURU]
Uh, well...
I mean, I really need you
to help weave the silk, Shuna.
But you're welcome to come
serve me in your spare time.
Anything to save me
from this tug-of-war match!
[giggles]
That sounds perfect!
So you're saying
that you do want my help.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, you bet! I'd love it.
Help, they're gonna stretch me
out like a piece of chewing gum!
Right, allow us
to get out of your way
so you can focus on work.
[RIMURU groans softly]
[door opens]
Oh. Good afternoon.
Have you come here to eat lunch?
[RIMURU] Yep. Shion said
she made me a special meal
and I'm dyin' to try it.
[ALL gasp]
♪
[RIMURU]
Are you guys gonna join us?
Uh, you know, I'm actually
not that hungry.
Right, we just came here
for tea.
I'll pass.
[RIMURU] Whoa, since when could
Souei use the Body Double Skill?
[SOUEI] Excuse me.
I should really scout the area.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[groans]
I'll go and fetch your lunch.
[RIMURU]
Uh, okay.
♪
Hmm.
[RIMURU]
Is there a reason
he's sweatin' bullets
over there?
Wait a second, don't tell me
this is gonna be
that overused trope.
The one where
the seemingly-skilled hot woman
turns out to suck at cooking?
Hope you're hungry.
Feel free to dig in.
[RIMURU]
Why trope, why?!
[stomach growling]
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
"Not hungry," yeah right!
Those cowards knew Shion
was a terrible cook
and left me to die!
Lord Rimuru,
aren't you going to eat?
[RIMURU]
Look at me, you jerk!
Look me in the eyes
before I die!
And the old man is just
casually hiding his presence!
Traitors!
[SHION]
Here, don't forget your spoon.
[BENIMARU]
Forgive me, Lord Rimuru.
[HAKUROU]
It's all part of your training.
Whew. I don't know about you,
but I'm starvin'.
[SHION]
Hurry, eat up.
♪
Right. It looks delicious.
I know. Thanks.
[RIMURU] I mean, it's probably
not poisonous, right?
It won't kill me?!
[groans]
[muffled groan]
[RIMURU]
Okay, relax.
There's no way this food
just creepily smiled at me.
It's just my imagination.
[GREAT SAGE]
A simulacrum.
The tendency to see
a face in anything
with three distinctly
visible points.
[RIMURU]
Thanks.
But I didn't really
want an explanation.
[groaning]
[SHION sighs]
[RIMURU] Great Sage,
please help me!
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
If you close your eyes
and insert the spoon
at an angle to your right,
you are less likely to die.
[groaning softly]
[RIMURU]
Whatever saves my slife!
[gulps]
That's weird.
[groaning]
[GOBTA screaming]
[GOBTA groaning]
[gasps]
[groaning continues]
[gagging]
Um... Oopsie.
-Shion.
-Yes, sir?
The next time you decide
to make a meal,
get Benimaru's approval first.
[BENIMARU gasps]
[BENIMARU]
Is this some sort of punishment?
[RIMURU]
Take that.
Enjoy supervising her, jerk.
It's all in
Benimaru's hands now.
Hopefully, we won't lose
any more good monsters
the way we lost Gobta.
Meanwhile, Gabiru the lizardman
continued his quest
to recruit goblins
from the other nearby villages.
You could say it was
his persuasive nature
that won them over,
or the goblins' fear
of an orc invasion.
Whatever the case, the goblins
were happy to cooperate.
[LIZARDMAN]
Hmm.
Altogether, we've recruited
about 7,000 goblins.
Way to go, Sir Gabiru.
You're a great negotiator.
Who me?
No, it just so happens
my best efforts
are being rewarded, is all.
Oh, pish posh.
You're obviously talented.
Obviously.
You need to have
more confidence in yourself.
[LIZARDMAN]
Indeed.
You're the future chieftain
of the lizardmen, after all.
Sure. I guess.
[GABIRU]
That's true.
I mustn't forget
how great I am!
Right! Anyway, where shall
we head to next?
Are there any other villages
awaiting my greatness?
Actually, there is one more
goblin settlement close by.
[LIZARDMAN]
Yes, but the residents
of the previous village
had some odd things
to say about it.
What sorts of things?
Believe it or not, they claim
the goblins there
have managed
to tame direwolves.
Wait, are you pulling
my tail right now?
What a ridiculous claim.
I agree.
And to make it
even more ludicrous,
they say that the goblins
are led by a slime monster.
What?!
That's a rather
unlikely scenario.
Still, if it's true
and we can control the slime,
then we'll be able to
control the direwolves, too!
-That's true.
-How clever.
You are such
a talented leader, sir.
I am so glad
I chose to follow you.
[chuckles]
That's right, just leave
all the thinking to me, men!
[LIZARDMAN 2]
All hail Sir Gabiru!
-Here's to Gabiru.
-Gabiru!
[cheering]
Gabiru! Gabiru!
-Gabiru! Gabiru!
-[laughs]
[KAIJIN]
Really?
You choose the best heat level
for tempering by instinct?
Sure. I can tell
just by the color of the flame.
Oh, yeah? No measuring?
I measure it the second time
around, just to be certain.
[KAIJIN] Right,
because if the outside
is cold, it won't be pliable.
So, do you measure...
[RIMURU] Kurobe and Kajin
hit it off as soon as they met.
They've been going on
about this blacksmith
mumbo jumbo for over two hours.
[KUROBE]
Oh, if you're interested,
I can show you
the best dirt to use.
[RIMURU]
I came in to check on them,
but I haven't been able to find
a good time to excuse myself,
so I'm still here.
-Right?
-Isn't forging fascinating?
[RIMURU]
Uh, sure.
[KUROBE]
So, tell me about the water
you use during tempering.
Is Lord Rimuru in here?
[RIMURU]
Nice timing.
-What's up, my dude?
-It's trouble.
There's a lizardman envoy
just outside the village.
[BENIMARU]
Lord Rimuru.
Would it be all right
if we accompanied you?
We want to know
what the lizardmen are here for.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, for sure.
Now then,
are we dealing
with friends or foes?
Which one's the envoy?
-[thudding]
-[RIMURU gasps]
[RIMURU]
Talk about your dramatic entry.
[GABIRU grunts]
♪
Hmph. [grunts]
Ho there, fellow monsters,
I am Gabiru of the lizardmen.
From now on,
you will all serve under me,
and consider it a great honor!
[LIZARDMAN 1]
Yay! Sir Gabiru.
-So great!
-[LIZARDMAN 2] Woo-hoo!
[LIZARDMAN 3]
You're amazing.
[ALL]
Huh?
Pay close attention
and savor this moment forever.
You have the great privilege
of speaking
with the future chieftain
of the lizardmen personally.
You may bow!
[ALL]
Huh?
[RIMURU]
"You will all serve under me,
and consider it a great honor"?
As if! What a delusional doofus.
And, Shion, please calm down.
You're gonna make me go
from slime to slim
if you don't stop squeezing!
[SHION] I'm so sorry, my lord.
Please forgive me!
[grunts]
Uh, anyway,
you said that your name
was Gabiru, correct?
This request to serve
under you seems a little sudden.
Seriously, are you really
gonna make me
spell things out for you?
You must have heard
the rumors by now.
What rumors?
[GABIRU]
My people have witnessed
the beginnings
of an orc invasion,
they're trying to take over
the Great Forest of Jura.
[RIMURU]
Uh, oh?
Which is why it would be
prudent for you
to come and fight under me.
I, the illustrious Gabiru,
can protect you!
Serve me,
and you weaklings will have
nothing to fear from the orcs!
I am strong!
Much stronger...
[weakly]
than you.
Wow.
Hmm.
Yeah, I don't see any goblins.
How strange.
But this was supposed
to be a goblin village.
In that regard, I don't see
anyone weak around here, either.
[RIMURU] Well, if it's true
that the orcs are invading,
maybe forming a united front
with the lizardmen
isn't a bad idea.
[sighs]
[RIMURU] But I'm not totally
sold on Gabiru as an ally.
He seems kinda dumb.
"What one should really fear
is not a competent enemy,
but an incompetent ally."
Was it Napoleon who said that?
So, ahem!
I have been told that
there are some among you
who have managed
to tame direwolves.
Those of you who have
will be my officers.
Go forth
and fetch them for me.
[SHION grunting]
[RIMURU] Oh, crap!
Stop pissing her off, dude!
[BENIMARU]
My lord, shall I dispose of him?
[RIMURU chuckles nervously]
Yes! No, I was just kidding!
Listen, we didn't exactly
tame the direwolves.
I just made them
into our allies.
A mere slime?
Come now, don't be ridiculous.
[RIMURU]
Ugh. Ranga.
[RANGA]
Yes, master.
[RANGA growling]
[RIMURU]
This guy wants to talk to you.
Please hear him out.
[RANGA growling]
Right.
[grunts]
[LIZARDMEN gasping]
[BENIMARU]
Wait. Was he always that big?
[RIMURU]
Yeah, that's his true size.
It's a little more suited
for getting a message
across to unwilling listeners.
[RANGA] My master has ordered me
to hear what you have to say.
Go on, I'm listening.
So does that mean
you're the leader
of the direwolves?
[RIMURU]
Uh...
Wow, the other lizardmen
are cowering in fear.
But this dude
seems to be holding his own.
Still dumb as a rock, though.
Your coat is beautiful.
Your eyes, so keen.
It's obvious that you're
a magnificent creature.
And yet,
you debase yourself by choosing
to serve a pitiful little slime?
[RIMURU]
Excuse you?
[grunts]
My dear friend, I worry
that you may have been deceived.
But fear not,
what this slime has done to you
is truly unforgivable.
So, I shall defeat him for you!
Get him, Sir Gabiru!
Yes, show them
how powerful you are.
Kick his butt, sir.
All together.
[cheering]
Gabiru! Gabiru! Gabiru!
Yes!
-Gabiru! Gabiru! Gabiru!
-All right! Whoo!
-Gabiru! Gabiru!
-[RANGA] You must be joking.
You dare to insult my master?
[growling]
-[chanting continues]
-[RIMURU] Dumb move.
-[RANGA growling]
-[RIMURU] Rest in peace, Gabiru.
[LIZARDMEN cheering]
Gabiru!
[GOBTA]
♪ Fa la la la ♪
[low growling]
[growling]
Oh, hey!
What are you guys up to?
[BENIMARU]
Gobta?
[RIMURU]
Whoa! I thought you died.
Come on,
why would you think that?
I'm as strong as a bulldeer.
[GREAT SAGE] Notice.
To counteract Shion's cooking,
Gobta has gained
the Poison Resistance Skill.
[RIMURU]
That's cool.
Even I don't have that skill,
I'm actually kind of impressed.
Wow, really?!
[chuckling]
[RANGA]
Perfect timing.
Huh?
[groans]
What the heck is going on here?!
[groaning]
[RANGA] Lizard, if you can
defeat this hobgoblin,
then I'll consider joining you.
Why me?
[RIMURU]
Good boy, Ranga!
I can't believe how calm he is.
Naturally, if he fought Gabiru,
he'd destroy him.
Sure, I'll fight him.
I take it the poor little slime
can't bear the shame of losing?
[GABIRU chuckles]
Whatever spares your pride.
[RIMURU grunts]
[RIMURU] Gobta, don't hold back!
Crush him!
So, hey, why am I the one
fighting, again?
[RIMURU]
'Cause if you win,
I'll talk to Kurobe about making
a special weapon for you.
Are you serious?!
That sort of motivates me.
If you lose, you have
to eat Shion's cooking.
I will destroy this lizard!
Wait, so my cooking
is considered punishment?
[RIMURU groaning]
[yelling]
[LIZARDMEN]
Go get him, Sir Gabiru!
Are you ready, little one?
[yelling]
You may begin.
[howling]
-[cheering] Gabiru! Gabiru!
-[scoffs] Not to boast,
but we lizardmen are descendants
of the great Dragons.
You have no chance.
[grunting]
Hmm?
♪
[GABIRU screams]
[LIZARDMEN gasp]
What? How dare you?
Impossible. Where'd he go?
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[RIMURU]
I can't believe my Magic Sense.
Did Gobta use Shadow Movement?
Whew. [pants]
[RANGA]
It's finished.
The fight is over.
Gobta is the winner!
-Nicely played.
-Well done!
Good job.
[chuckling]
[RIGURD]
Bravo!
-[GOBTA] Go higher!
-[RIGURD] Bravo!
[RANGA]
Excellent work.
I knew I saw
promise in you, Gobta.
[RIGURD] You did very well
and showed them
never to underestimate
a hobgoblin.
[SHION]
I misjudged you,
for that I'll pretend like
I didn't hear you
insult my cooking earlier.
Just this once, you get a pass.
[BENIMARU]
He's certainly come a long way
since he fought against us
back in the forest.
[HAKUROU]
This young hobgoblin
may have a talent
that's worth nurturing.
[RIMURU]
Wait, is it possible
that Gobta's actually
some sort of prodigy?
Also, did everyone besides me
believe that he'd actually win?
I thought...
[groaning]
You'll regret this insult.
How dare youse hurt
one of our guys?
Since you attacked us first,
youse going to pay now.
[RIMURU]
They'd get mad over Gobta losing
and beat the snot out of Gabiru.
[RIMURU sighs]
No worries, I'm a decent actor,
I'll just play along.
This was all part of my plan.
Great job, Gobta!
As promised, I'll have Kurobe
make you a weapon.
[GOBTA]
Thank you, sir!
[RIMURU] As for you all,
our man has won this battle.
[LIZARDMEN gasp]
[RIMURU]
If you want our town's help
in defeating the orc army,
I'm willing to consider it,
but we won't serve you.
Take your leader
and leave for today.
[GABIRU groans]
Well, this isn't over.
Yes, that's right.
You haven't seen
the last of us.
[sighs]
We'll...
We'll remember this!
[RIMURU]
That was weird.
I guess we need
to plan our next move.
♪
[SOUEI]
There were 200,000.
It appears that the main army is
marching north along the river.
And my guess is that based on
the movements of this army
and a detached force,
they'll regroup
in the marshlands.
Wait, are you talking
about the ones east of here,
in the lizardmen's territory?
[SOUEI]
Mm-hmm.
Two hundred thousand.
That's such an obscene number
I can't even imagine it.
[RIMURU sighs]
What exactly is it
that these orcs are after?
Who knows?
To be honest, orcs aren't
very intelligent monsters
to begin with.
If there's something
driving this invasion
other than their instincts,
then it would also be safe to
assume someone is backing them.
But who would wanna
control orcs?
Someone like a Demon Lord?
♪
It could even be Gelmud.
He tried to recruit you,
so it's possible
it might be connected.
But it's not like
I have proof to base that on.
And even if it is
a Demon Lord,
that doesn't mean it's the one
who made Shizu suffer either.
[BENIMARU sighs]
I can't speak about
the whole Demon Lord part.
-Except...
-Except?
Except that it would
confirm my suspicions.
An Orc Lord.
[RIMURU] Wait, you mean
the Unique Monster
that only appears
once every few centuries?
[BENIMARU] Yes. I can't imagine
that an ordinary orc
would be capable of leading
such an impressive army.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
We should lean
on the side of caution.
We can't afford mistakes.
[RIMURU]
I agree.
[gasps]
What's wrong?
[SOUEI] One of the body doubles
I had scouting the area
has had an encounter.
Uh, 'kay?
Someone's requesting an audience
with you, Lord Rimuru.
How should I respond?
Who is it?
I've already had
my fill of weirdos today
because of Gabiru,
I don't want any more surprises.
Well, I'm not sure
I'd call them a "weirdo,"
but it is a rather
unusual encounter.
You see...
it's a dryad.
[ALL gasp]
Shut your face!
Aren't dryads those
hot tree spirit babes
that you always see
in video games?!
But it's been several decades
since the last time
we've seen a dryad,
I wonder why one would
just suddenly appear now?
Uh, okay. Bring her in.
Right.
[gasps]
♪
[DRYAD]
Greetings, ruler of monsters,
and all of those
who are loyal to him.
Please pardon
my unannounced visit.
I am a dryad
from the Forest of Jura,
please call me Treyni.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
My name's Rimuru Tempest.
Likewise. Nice to meet you.
So what brings you
to our village?
[TREYNI] I have come
because I need
to request a favor from you.
A favor?
Rimuru Tempest,
as the ruler of monsters,
please help us.
We need you to defeat
the Orc Lord.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"The Gears Spin Out of Control."