[NARRATOR]
Rimuru and his friends
are traveling north,
following the Ameld River.
They're headed for Dwargon,
the Kingdom of the Dwarves,
hoping to find artisans
who can help make clothing
and houses for the Goblins.
His band includes Rigur
and two other goblins,
as well as their guide Gobta,
who has apparently
made the trip before.
The Tempest Wolves who evolved
from the Direwolves
run as fast as the wind.
[RIMURU] Be careful not to
push yourselves too hard!
[RANGA]
Right!
[RIMURU screaming]
That didn't mean
go faster, Ranga!
[panting]
[RIMURU]
Hey, Rigur.
I was wondering, who was it
that named your brother?
Sir, I'm told
that he received his name
from a passing demon
called Lord Gelmud.
He saw promise in him.
[RIMURU]
Gel what?
Oh, Lord Gelmud.
He's from the Demon Lord's army.
[RIMURU] Oh. Hold up,
"Demon Lord's Army"? Demon Lord?
Back in the cave
Veldora mentioned a hero, too.
Hopefully I don't run
into either of them.
Sounds like nothing but trouble.
[gasps]
♪
[RIMURU]
Say, Ranga.
[RANGA]
Yes?
[RIMURU] Since I was the one
who killed your dad,
do you ever think
about avenging him?
Like taking me out
or whatever?
It's something
I've been kinda worried about.
[RANGA]
I have thought about it.
But though I lost my father,
you spared the rest of us,
even after defeating our clan,
and then you gave us a new name.
I feel nothing but gratitude.
There's no room for resentment.
Our pack is loyal to you
and you alone.
You are our only master.
-[RIMURU] Gobta.
-Yes?
Any chance you can tell me more
about where we're headed?
Uh, well, for starters,
its official title
is technically
the "Armed Nation
of Dwargon."
It's a beautiful city carved out
of a natural cave system,
where dwarves,
elves, humans,
and other species live
and work together in harmony.
[RIMURU]
Elves?!
[WOMEN chuckling]
[RIMURU]
Like, lady elves?
Oh, and the city's leader
is Gazel Dwargo,
also known
as the Hero King,
supposedly, he's greatly
admired by his people.
[RIMURU]
Elves.
-[WOMAN chuckling]
-Elves!
[RIGUR]
Lord Rimuru?
[RIMURU] So, anyway, is it cool
for monsters like me
to go into Dwargon
or are there rules?
Please, there's
no need to worry.
Dwargon is a neutral zone
and a free-trade area.
By the king's command,
all fighting is prohibited
within the city limits.
[RIMURU]
Gotcha.
Dwargon's military
keeps the peace,
so we have them to thank.
They're a force
to reckoned with.
It's said that the Dwarven army
has been undefeated
for a thousand years.
[RIMURU] Seriously?!
Color me impressed.
It sounds like no one
would be stupid enough
to get on that king's bad side.
Last time I was there,
someone picked a fight
with me outside of the gate.
I'm sure we'll be fine.
Don't worry, my lord.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
I can't put
my gelatinous finger on it,
but I feel like a red flag
just went up.
Nice, they're ready.
These smell delicious.
[RIMURU] It's said
that for a goblin on foot,
it can take a total
of two months or more
to walk to the Dwarven Kingdom.
However, thanks to Ranga
and the other Tempest Wolves,
Rimuru's party made
the same journey in three days.
I see, so that's where
the Elves,
uh, that is,
the Dwarves, live, huh?
I can't wait to meet
some gorgeous Elves,
uh, I mean, I can't wait to meet
some super-skilled Dwarves!
[RIGUR] Are you sure
you only wanna take Gobta
into the city
with you, my lord?
[RIMURU] Yep. A big group will
just draw unwanted attention.
So, Gobta can show me around.
-But, sir--
-Relax, we'll be fine.
[RANGA]
Please don't go.
[RIMURU]
Don't worry.
We'll be back as soon as we can.
You guys just chill here, okay?
Be careful, my lord.
[howling]
[indistinct chatter]
[RIMURU] Check out this line.
Security must be strict.
Yeah, but once we get inside,
we're pretty much free
to do whatever we want.
[RIMURU]
Whatever we want?
[WOMEN chuckling]
[MAN]
Well, what do we have here?
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Looks like a couple
of scrawny monsters.
There aren't any rules about
fighting outside the city,
so they're fair game.
[RIMURU]
And there it is, the red flag.
I should've called this.
Hey, Gobta.
Did this happen last time?
Uh-huh, it did, sir.
I was waiting in line to get in
when I got beat up
by some humans.
Unfortunately, that's the fate
of weak monsters.
[RIMURU]
Maybe it's time to change that.
You dumb monsters
better stop ignoring us
or you'll regret it.
Now hold on, a talking slime
monster's a pretty rare sight.
We could make a fortune
selling it.
[RIMURU] Gobta, do you remember
the first rule I told you?
Yes.
I recall rule number one
was we should never
attack a human, sir.
[RIMURU] Correct.
So, I want you to close
your eyes and cover your ears.
Do not look this way, got it?
I understand!
[RIMURU]
Okay, then.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[RIMURU]
Listen, dummies.
I'm feeling generous,
so if you leave right now,
I'll spare your lives.
[grunts]
You must be joking, what are you
gonna do, get us all slimy?!
Yeah, shut your
nonexistent trap!
We were gonna let you live,
but since you've pissed us off
you'd better say
your prayers, monster!
[RIMURU] They're as weak
as their comebacks.
Wait, are you threatening me?
How bold of you.
Of course, we are,
you stupid slime!
[RIMURU] Oh! You think
I'm just a mere slime?
I am. I totally am.
[laughs]
What gave you the impression
that I was such a weak monster?
Fine, then. I guess I'll have
to show you my true form.
[growling]
Huh?
Did my Mimicry skill evolve?
[scoffs]
All you did was
change your appearance!
There's no way you can scare us
off with your cheap tricks.
[RIMURU] This is so annoying,
just run away already.
Whatever. Let's do this!
Come at me, bruh!
Ha! Well, it's your funeral.
Yeah, let's get him, guys!
[RIMURU]
Where'd they come from?
Die!
Slash attack!
Heavy Hitting Cut!
Cast fireball!
Magic Wall, go!
[yells]
-[MAN] It bounced off?
-But that's impossible.
His fur is too tough!
[RIMURU growling]
Oh, I think I felt an itch.
Holy hell.
I thought I was gonna die!
Mimicry is the bomb!
[panting]
-[RIMURU] Now it's my turn.
-[MEN gasping]
[growling]
[screaming]
[yelling]
[screaming continues]
Unh. Oopsie.
[GREAT SAGE]
Menace attack damage report:
Sixteen people fled.
Sixty-eight became confused.
Ninety-two fainted.
Thirty-four soiled themselves.
[RIMURU] I really could have
passed on the last detail.
-[CAPTAIN] Hey!
-[RIMURU gasps]
[growls]
Stop right there!
Huh?
[CAPTAIN]
A slime?
[RIMURU]
Tee-hee.
[snoring]
[RIMURU]
We're in the middle of a crisis
and he's taking a nap?
Sheesh, some guide
he turned out to be.
-[CAPTAIN] Well?
-[RIMURU] Uh, right!
Actually, that's everything.
[sighs]
Since you're a slime monster
and a goblin,
they probably attacked
thinking you'd be easy targets.
[RIMURU] All I wanted to do
was scare them away.
I'm really sorry, I never meant
to cause you so much trouble.
Okay.
Everything you told me matches
up with the witness reports.
Just this once, I'll let you--
[GUARD]
Captain, we've got trouble!
There was an Armorsaurus attack
in the mine!
Call the Suppression Force.
They're en route, sir.
But Garm and his brothers were
in the mine gathering magic ore
and I'm afraid
they've been badly injured.
Do we have potions?
Not enough.
We had to donate most of them
to the war effort.
[grunts]
Well, we have to do something,
those guys are like
brothers to me.
There's no time to waste,
start looking for more potions.
-[RIMURU] Um, sir?
-Search the entire city!
-[RIMURU] Sir?
-Huh?
Ugh. Hey, you weren't supposed
to leave the barrel!
[RIMURU] But if I had
stayed in the barrel,
how would I have done that?
You guys need this, right?
What's that?
[RIMURU] Healing potion.
The best around.
You can drink it
or apply it directly.
Huh?
Hmm.
You're welcome to use it
on your men.
Huh?
Hold on, Captain.
Are you really gonna trust
that slime's potion?
Yes, I'll have to.
Let's hurry up.
Yes, right away, sir.
You, get back in that cell.
[RIMURU] He was really worried
about those dudes in the mine.
Seems like a good guy.
A cradle!
A diamond!
Hand drum!
A boat!
And now...
Tokyo tower!
[snoring]
[RIMURU]
Ahh!
Gobta's Unique Skill
must be the power
to sleep through anything.
[footsteps approaching]
[CAPTAIN] You saved them.
Thank you!
Are you the one
that gave us that potion?
-We're in your debt.
-[RIMURU] No prob.
My arm was almost ripped off,
even if I had survived,
there's no way
I'd be able to work.
-Thanks a lot, pal.
-[RIMURU] You're welcome.
Mm-hmm.
-Mm-hmm.
-[RIMURU] Use your words!
Thanks again for your help.
We owe you one.
Mm-hmm.
[RIMURU]
Am I free?
Yeah, of course you are.
I gotta tell you,
that healing potion you gave us
is the most remarkable thing
I've ever seen.
I can't thank you enough,
and if you ever need a favor,
you can count on me.
[RIMURU]
Well, in that case...
Hmm?
I see. That's an easy fix.
I'll introduce you
to the best blacksmith I know.
[RIMURU]
Thanks, that'd be awesome!
[CAPTAIN]
There's no need to thank me.
I'm happy to help out.
[indistinct chatter]
[WOMAN]
Welcome.
[RIMURU]
Whoa-oa-oa!
The city of Dwargon is so cool!
Everything's so advanced
compared to the Goblin Village.
-[CAPTAIN] This way.
-Huh?
Don't get lost now.
[RIMURU]
Wow!
There's so much incredible
detail in every piece!
Check out that sword.
Is it actually shining?
Is it magic?
Yeah, you got a good eye.
I know the guy
who made this piece.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[CAPTAIN] It's the blacksmith
I told you about.
[RIMURU]
Aw, yeah!
[CAPTAIN] Here we are!
Trust me, this guy is great.
Hey, bro, It's me. You busy?
[RIMURU]
Bro?
Hey, Kaido. Give me one sec.
Yeah, sure.
[RIMURU]
Sorry to interrupt you.
That's Kaijin. My older brother.
[RIMURU] Whoa. That dude's
definitely tough as nails.
-[MAN 1] Huh?
-[MAN 2] Uh!
[RIMURU]
Huh? Oh.
[KAIJIN]
Hmm?
Oh, a slime.
Do you guys know each other?
Indeed we do,
it's the one from yesterday.
It's the slime
we told you about,
he gave us that
great healing potion.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, I've heard a lot about you.
Thanks so much. I'm grateful.
[RIMURU] Come on now,
you're making me blush,
ain't no thang.
Or is it?
[laughing]
So, uh, what did you need?
Hmm. Yes, I see.
That's a conundrum. I'm sorry.
I'm just too backed up
to help out.
Thanks to that
dimwitted minister,
I've got more work
than I can possibly handle.
[RIMURU]
What do you mean?
It's likely we'll be
going to war soon,
so he wants 20 longswords.
All by the end of the week.
To make things even worse,
I'm short on materials
so I've only got one done.
Dummy.
Why didn't you say
it was an impossible request?
[RIMURU]
Yeah, why?
Don't call me a dummy.
Besides, I actually did try
to turn it down at first.
But that snooty Minister Vesta
just wouldn't let it go.
How disappointing.
I've always heard
that the great Kaijin
is the best blacksmith
in the entire city of Dwargon.
Yet he's unable to handle
such a menial task?
No way I could ever let
an insult like that slide.
My pride's on the line.
[RIMURU]
Sounds kinda like my old boss.
I guess workplace politics
are alive and well
in this world, too.
So, you need materials?
Yeah, there's a particular item
that I need called magic ore.
It's actually what we were
mining for yesterday.
But then that Armorsaurus
showed up.
Mm-hmm.
[RIMURU]
I see.
Still though,
it's not like there was much
left there to mine anyway.
The ore's all been
cleared out, so...
Mm-hmm.
[KAIJIN] Even if I could
get my hands on the materials,
it'd take two weeks
to make 20 swords.
To be honest,
I don't have enough time.
Unfortunately,
I only have five days
to deliver every one of
those swords to the king.
Every smith in the kingdom
has been asked to complete
the same project,
and if for some reason
we can't do it,
then they've threatened
to revoke our certifications.
That's awful.
[RIMURU]
Man, that sucks for you.
Wait. If it's magic ore,
could it be one and the same?!
-[laughs]
-Hmm?
[laughing]
Hey, old man.
[grunts]
Here. Can you use this?
Hmm? Hold on, now.
Hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on!
That's a huge chunk
of magic ore.
And it's unbelievably
pure, to boot.
[gasping]
[RIMURU]
Check again.
Are you sure
it's a chunk of magic ore?
Huh?
Ohh! By the king's name!
It's already been processed
into a cluster of magisteel.
[RIMURU]
Precisely.
I'll be able to create
some amazing swords
with a piece this pure,
in fact, the entire cluster
is extremely valuable.
(clears throat) Um, but wait,
are you certain I can have this?
I mean, of course I'd be
happy to compensate you.
[RIMURU] Let's see.
It is a lot to part with.
-[whistles]
-[KAIJIN] What is it you want?
I'll give you anything
within my power.
[RIMURU] Actually, I was hoping
you'd say that.
[gasps]
I'd like you to gather
some artisans for me.
Ones who'd be willing
to travel to my village
and maybe teach us their trades.
Is that seriously all you want?
Yeah, we're kind of
lacking the clothing
and shelter thing
that every village needs.
We'll probably need
extra clothes,
as well as some weapons
and armor in the future, too.
[laughs]
You've got yourself a deal.
But, Kaijin...
Even if we started
on those swords right away...
Uh...
[RIMURU]
Can you finish on time?
Well, I have to at least
give it a shot.
All right, boys,
let's get going!
-Yeah!
-Mm-hmm.
Huh. Great Sage,
you got a minute?
[GREAT SAGE]
Yes.
-[RIMURU] Hey, old man.
-Hmm?
You said you've got
one sword made, right?
Can I please see it?
Um, yeah, sure.
[RIMURU]
It's magnificent.
Even in my untrained
slime eye,
I can tell you possess
an admirable skill.
Uh... Is the blade shining?
Yes, because it has
a magisteel core.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[KAIJIN]
How do I explain?
A sword with that sort of core
can change and evolve
depending on its user.
[RIMURU]
Awesome!
So cool, I wish
I could get Kaijin
to come back
to the village with us.
Uh, but for that to happen...
Hey, mind if I borrow this?
[gasps]
-[KAIJIN] Hey!
-The sword!
-He ate it?
-[gasps]
Hmm?
Why would you do that?
[RIMURU]
Just trust me.
Okay, analyze away.
[GREAT SAGE]
Analyzing: Longsword.
Analysis complete.
[RIMURU] Now, use some magisteel
to make a few copies.
[GREAT SAGE]
Producing copy.
Successful.
[all gasp]
[gasping]
[RIMURU]
I give you 20 longswords.
All with magisteel cores.
[ALL]
What?!
[RIMURU]
A party?
[KAIJIN] Yeah, I would never
have made my delivery on time
if it weren't for you.
[RIMURU] Nonsense, you don't
have to do that for me.
Aw, come on.
It'll be fun, there's gonna be
lots of cute elf girls there.
-[RIMURU] Elves?!
-Yeah!
It's a place called
Butterflies of the Night!
And it's loaded
with beautiful women.
They'll wait on you
hand and foot all night long!
-Butterflies.
-Hmm. Hmm.
Speak, man!
Come on, you have to go,
it won't be a party
without you, Rimuru.
That's right!
[RIMURU] Well, since you insist,
it'd be rude for me not to go.
-[cheering]
-[laughter]
[RIMURU]
Sheesh!
What am I gonna do
with you guys?!
[WOMEN chuckling]
♪
[door opens]
[WOMAN]
It's Kaijin. Good to see you.
[ALL]
Welcome, masters.
[RIMURU]
Holy crap!
Elves!
Elves.
E-I-L-F!
I mean, Elves!
Aw, cutie!
[RIMURU exclaiming]
Oh, yes!
Hey, no fair.
Here. Come hang out with me.
[RIMURU] Oh, my gah!
Her dress is so thin.
Wow, it's like
super soft and bouncy.
[RIMURU] I'm pretty sure
that's my line.
Ahhh!
I think I've died and gone
straight to honker heaven.
Boobs are amazing.
These were worth the wait.
[KAIJIN] For a guy who initially
didn't wanna come here,
you sure seem happy now.
[RIMURU]
Huh? Uh...
Uh, don't be ridiculous!
[all laugh]
[grunting]
Okay, then, who's ready
for a drink?
[MEN]
Me!
Hmm.
[RIMURU] During this time,
I was living my best life.
I mean, I had the most
awesome seat in the house.
Sometimes life is filled with
huge, bouncy, peaks and valleys.
But you know the saying,
all good things
must come to an end.
That's life for you.
Right?
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Hero King, Gazel Dwargo."