[SATORU]
So, what are we gonna do?
[VELDORA]
Hmm?
[SATORU] You know, about this
Unlimited Imprisonment thing.
Now that we're buddies,
I feel bad
that you've been
stuck here alone
for the past 300 years.
"Buddies"?
Is that a dragon version
of puppy dog eyes?
Come on, man, that look's
only cute coming from a girl.
I'm willing to listen
to any ideas you have.
As it stands now,
I probably only have
100 years or so
before my magic
completely runs out.
My magicules have been
leaking out of me.
That explains why this cave
is magicule central.
No wonder there's valuable herbs
and ore galore.
What happens when
you run outta juice?
[VELDORA]
Nothing really.
[SATORU]
What do you mean by "nothing"?
[scoffs]
I'll probably just die.
Oh. That's rough.
Three hundred years
of complete solitude
followed by dying alone?
[sighs]
Uh, well, it's worth a try.
[VELDORA]
Hmm.
[SATORU]
Great Sage,
use Predator on
the Unlimited Imprisonment.
[GREAT SAGE]
The attempt has failed.
[SATORU] Should've known
it wouldn't be that easy.
It's hopeless.
[SATORU sighs]
Isn't there anything we can do?
[GREAT SAGE]
Examining possibilities.
Hey! It's rude to ignore me
to just talk to your own skill.
[SATORU]
Jealous?
[GREAT SAGE]
Survey completed.
Possibilities include...
-[VELDORA] Hmm.
-[SATORU] Uh-huh.
Yeah, that makes sense.
So, here's what
I've got for you.
We have to analyze
the Unlimited Imprisonment
from both sides, then we might
be able to remove it.
[VELDORA]
Oh? Hold on.
I can't analyze it from my side.
The hero also sealed my skills,
so I won't be much help.
Then just give me the data
and I'll analyze it
from my side.
[VELDORA] Okay, but that could
take quite a while.
I wouldn't want you to have to
wait around that whole time.
Uh, not that it would
bother me or anything.
[SATORU]
That's a good point.
I was thinking that maybe
I'd like to try
and find others from my world.
[VELDORA]
Of course.
There is one thing we could try.
Uh, wh-what is it?
How's about you get
in my stomach?
[dings]
See, I can use my skills,
Great Sage and Predator
to analyze
Unlimited Imprisonment.
Meanwhile you can try to
destroy it from the inside.
You'll be safe and sound
inside my slime tummy
and probably won't
disappear permanently.
What do you think?
[VELDORA laughing]
[laughing menacingly]
[shrieks]
Now that sounds like
it could be interesting.
Let's do it! I'm willing.
I trust you completely, friend.
Just like that, huh?
No questions asked?
Well, sure.
Breaking through
Unlimited Imprisonment together
sounds like it could be fun.
And my only other choice is to
wait here for you to come back.
Alone.
I guess, and two
is better than one.
Let's do this thing!
[VELDORA]
Yes!
-[SATORU laughs]
-[VELDORA] Hmm?
Okay.
So I'll use Predator and--
-Hold on a moment.
-Huh?
Before you proceed, I'd like
to give you a proper name.
I think you should
give me one, too.
[SATORU]
Huh?
By doing so, it engraves
onto our souls
the fact that we are equals.
It's what humans often refer
to as a "family name,"
but the name I give you
will offer my divine protection.
Currently, you are nameless.
So, this will mark you
as a monster with power.
[SATORU]
A monster with a name, huh?
Sounds cool.
[VELDORA]
Indeed it does.
Now give me a good name.
[SATORU]
I'll try.
Let's see, something cool.
Veldora the Storm Dragon...
Hmm. Storm...
I feel like if nothing else
it should at least be related
to that somehow.
And storm seems kinda obvious.
Oh!
How about "Tempest"?
That's a cool name, right?
"Tempest"?
That's what you chose?!
[groans]
Is it dumb?
It sounds fantastic!
From this day onward,
I am Veldora Tempest!
Yeesh, you scared me
for a second there.
Now I shall give you a name.
How about "Rimuru"?
[SATORU] Rimuru.
Yeah, sounds good.
Then you are now Rimuru Tempest!
[RIMURU]
At that moment,
I felt something shift
deep within my very soul.
It was as if the name itself
became permanently
engraved upon it.
I am Rimuru Tempest!
Rimuru.
Veldora Tempest.
Okay, well, I'm gonna
eat you now.
It's time to bust out
of that Unlimited Imprisonment!
[laughs]
Let's do it.
I'm sure we'll meet face-to-face
again in the near future.
We will.
Unique Skill: Predator!
[gasps]
That was easier
than I thought it would be.
Things are gonna be quiet
without Veldora.
[GREAT SAGE]
Would you like to analyze
the Unique Skill:
Unlimited Imprisonment?
Yes. Analyze away.
On that day,
a great tremor rocked the world.
The disappearance of Veldora
the Storm Dragon,
a Catastrophe-class monster,
was confirmed.
The cave where Veldora
had been sealed for so long
was located within
the Great Forest of Jura.
And on the outskirts
of that same forest
existed several
different countries.
One of those
aforementioned countries
was the Kingdom
of Blumund.
Have you heard about
the Storm Dragon yet?
Certainly you have.
I've heard a rumor or two.
[chuckles]
That's not surprising,
you are a Guild Master
after all.
Well, then, can you tell me
what measures the guild
intends to take
regarding this matter?
We hadn't intended to take
any sort of measures.
The disappearance of Veldora
will only serve
to galvanize the monsters,
which will be a problem
for everyone.
[sighs]
Honestly, I think
the real problem
you need to be worrying about
is the Eastern Kingdom.
With the dragon gone,
it's likely
they'll invade that region.
Yes, and if the Eastern Kingdom
does manage
to get through
the Great Forest of Jura,
the provinces
around it will fall
before we can even retaliate.
You look kind of tired.
Are you sleeping okay?
[chuckles]
As a favor to an old friend,
I suppose I could do
some investigating.
I will look into the state
of the forest,
and things
concerning the Kingdom.
Sounds good.
Thank you, Fuze.
[RIMURU] Veldora's disappearance
brought about chaos
in the surrounding countries,
causing quite a bit trouble
for humans and monsters alike.
Of course,
Rimuru had no way to know this.
I wonder how many days
have passed since I ate Veldora.
I meandered around for a while
trying to find my way
out of the cave.
I gobbled up any ore or plant
I came across
and stashed it
in my slime storage unit.
[humming]
[GREAT SAGE]
Skill: Water Movement acquired.
Skill: Water Blade acquired.
The acquired skills
Water Pressure Propulsion,
Water Movement and Water Blade
have been combined.
They have evolved
into an Extra Skill:
Water Manipulation.
[RIMURU]
I tried out all kinds of things
and learned some new skills.
And then I ran
into a new friend.
I knew from the moment we met
we were gonna be best buddies.
Psych.
[screaming]
[hisses]
[RIMURU]
This is bad.
Is it too late
to go the other way?
Hold up. This guy's not
any scarier than Veldora.
Maybe I'm overreacting.
Time to test out my mad skills.
Let's do this!
Water Blade!
[grunts]
Rimuru used Water Blade
and it was super effective.
I should be careful
who I use it on.
Pause.
If I were to use
my Predator skill
and eat
that snake monster thingy,
does that mean
I could analyze it
and learn
all of its abilities?
[grunting in effort]
Argh, down the hatch!
[groans]
Ew!
I can't taste but still, ew!
[groans]
[GREAT SAGE]
Analysis complete.
Skills: Poisonous Breath
and Sense Heat Source acquired.
You can now mimic
Black Serpent.
[gasps]
Cool, so I can breathe poison
and sense heat?
Sounds like that could
come in handy.
Oh, yes,
Predator is the bomb dot com!
That's it! I'm gonna acquire
all the skills!
♪
[growling]
[RIMURU]
Take this!
[grunting]
Note to self: Use sparingly.
♪
[grunts]
Water Blade! Water Blade!
Water Blade!
[sighs heavily]
[yelling like Tarzan]
[roaring]
♪
She sells seashells
down by the seashore.
How much wood
could a woodchuck chuck...
Thanks to the skills
I acquired from the Giant Bat,
I finally figured out
how to talk out loud.
[in robotic voice]
Take us to your leader.
We have come
from another planet.
[yells]
[grunts]
[groans]
Then, after several long weeks
of bouncing around
in that cave...
At last!
[shrieks]
A door that big has gotta
be the exit, right?
But how am I supposed
to open it?
Do I just Water Blade it
or what?
-[door rumbling]
-[gasps]
[gasping]
Huh?
[rumbling continues]
[sighs]
About time this sucker opened.
The keyhole is so freakin' rusty
it's impossible to use.
That's no big surprise.
This place has been vacant
for like 300 years or whatever.
[WOMAN]
We should still be careful
not to let our guard down.
If worse comes to worst, we can
always use our Escape Skill.
[RIMURU] Those are
the first humans I've seen.
I wonder
what they're doing here.
Adventuring, maybe?
How can I
understand them, though?
[GREAT SAGE] Answer:
The use of Magic Sense
can turn sound waves
that carry intention
into comprehensible words.
[RIMURU]
Makes sense, and that's good.
Foreign languages
are not my forte.
[GREAT SAGE]
And by producing sound waves
that carry your thoughts,
you may converse.
[RIMURU]
Ah!
But, uh, I'm a slime now.
Trying to talk to them might end
with yet another stabbing.
All right, come closer
so I can activate
my Stealth Arts.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Whoa!
He called that skill
"Stealth Arts."
Imagine the peeping
you could do!
What a disgraceful perv
that I absolutely want
to make friends with later!
[footsteps receding]
Are they gone?
[gasps]
What's wrong?
It's weird, I just thought
I sensed a monster nearby.
But nothing is there.
[birds chirping]
[RIMURU]
Finally, I left the cave.
It was the first time I'd seen
the sun since my last life.
I haven't heard anything
from Veldora since I ate him.
I'm worried he might be
gone for good,
but deep down I believe his
consciousness is still there.
After all, we made a promise.
I'll just have to go
on lots of adventures,
that way I'll have
some cool stories
to tell him
the next time we meet.
Ah, I haven't been
outside in forever.
The air tastes so sweet.
Not that I can taste.
Huh?
[gasping nervously]
[RIMURU]
Dear Veldora,
as it turns out,
I'll have a cool story
to tell you
a little sooner than I thought.
Scrawny bodies.
Beat-up weapons?
Strong One.
Please forgive me,
but do you have some sort of
business out here in the forest?
[RIMURU]
Uh, "Strong One"?
[groans]
-Does he mean me?
-Mm. Mm.
Right, I just need to produce
sound waves
carrying my thoughts.
[inhales sharply]
[screaming] Hi!
It's nice to meet you all!
[gasping]
[screaming]
My name is Rimuru
and I am a slime monster!
Ugh.
Please, sir, we're very aware
of just how much
strength you possess.
Spare us from
your all-powerful voice.
Oops, maybe I thought
a little too hard.
So, did you need something?
Well, we sensed a powerful
monster roaming around.
We came out here
to investigate it.
Whoa, so did you guys
already find it or what?
Surely you jest.
You can't fool us, sir.
Even if you have decided to take
on the form of a mere slime.
I'm the powerful monster?
Please excuse me, but seeing
as you're so strong,
we wanted to ask a favor.
Huh?
And that's how I got invited
to the Goblin Village.
"Village" might have
been a stretch though.
One sneeze from Veldora
and it'd be history.
[ELDER sighs]
Welcome to our humble town.
We are so honored
to have you here.
I am the elder of this village.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
So what kind of favor
did you guys need from me?
Hmm.
Have you perhaps noticed that
many of the monsters in the area
are unusually active
as of late?
No?
Our god, who has always
protected us,
suddenly disappeared without
a trace about a month ago.
As a result, the monsters
around this area
have started to continually
harass our poor village.
[RIMURU]
Their god?
Does he mean Veldora?
The timing fits.
He must have been keeping
the monsters at bay.
We tried to fight them
off ourselves,
but we simply
lack the numbers.
And that's why we asked you
to come here.
[RIMURU]
They think I can help them?
I don't know,
I'm just a lowly slime.
I'm really not that strong,
so I doubt I'd be too much help.
[laughs]
You're so modest.
And funny, too.
Oh?
There's no way
that a mere slime
would emit
such an overwhelming aura,
it's quite obvious that you're
a very powerful monster.
Aura?
What's he talking about?
Is that like power BO?
Yo, Great Sage.
Change Magic Sense's
perspective.
I'd like to look at myself.
[GREAT SAGE]
Changing perspective.
Whoa! Is that seriously
the aura around me?
I feel like I've been walking
around with my fly wide open.
This is so bad!
No wonder the goblins were
groveling back in the forest.
[chuckles]
You noticed, huh?
How wise of you.
But of course, Strong One,
there's no hiding
the rather formidable air
that surrounds you.
[RIMURU] I should have known
I wouldn't be able
to fool the village elder,
you've all shown a great deal
of potential.
Congratulations!
[grunts]
Whew, managed to suck it in.
Ah.
I understand now,
you were testing us.
Hopefully enough of our people
were appropriately frightened
at your powerful aura.
Uh, yeah, totally.
I'm actually impressed
you were brave enough
to speak to me at all.
What am I even talking about?
Come to think of it,
how did those humans
back in the cave not see me?
Maybe they're dumb?
[ELDER] You honor us
with your kind words.
Now, regarding the favor
we wished to ask you.
[RIMURU]
According to the goblins,
they've been having problems
with some nearby monsters
called Direwolves,
who attacked them from the east.
Many goblins lost their lives
in the battle against them.
These monsters are said to be
much stronger than the goblins.
And it takes ten of them
to have a chance
at beating one Direwolf.
There was a named warrior
among them
who served as the guardian
for their village.
Unfortunately, he was
killed in battle,
and his people
were left defenseless.
They were out of options.
Altogether, there are
about 100 Direwolves.
How many people do you have?
[ELDER]
Including women,
we have about 60
who can still fight.
[RIMURU]
Those aren't very good odds.
It's like a boss level
in a video game.
So that goblin warrior
went and fought against wolves
even though he knew
he couldn't possibly win?
Yes, even though he knew
the odds were against him.
He gave his life
so he could bring us
information on our foes.
You see, that warrior
was my son.
And his older brother.
[sobbing quietly]
[RIMURU]
Oh, man.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Elder.
I do have a question.
Uh, yes, sir?
What's in it for me,
like what would I get in return
if I decide to help you?
There has to be something
you guys can offer.
[shuddering]
[gasping softly]
It's not that I actually
want compensation.
But it also probably wouldn't
hurt to put on a bit of a show.
We, we could offer
our unfaltering loyalty.
Please, Strong One,
I'm begging you to grant us
your divine protection,
and in return our whole village
will swear to you.
We promise.
[RIMURU]
This brings back memories.
[TAMURA]
Please help me and I swear
I'll never ask you
for anything again.
All right already,
just calm down.
When it's all said and done,
I'm terrible at saying no.
-[wolf howling]
-[screaming]
[all gasp]
[gasps]
It's the Direwolves!
Oh, no, we're all gonna die!
What are we gonna do?!
They're going to eat
the whole village!
[FEMALE GOBLIN]
Should we run?
[MALE GOBLIN]
Where can we go?
[ELDER] Now, now, everyone,
just remain calm.
[RIMURU]
You have nothing to fear.
[GOBLINS gasp]
Because we're going to
defeat them.
[gasps]
So, you...
[scoffs]
In lieu of Veldora
the Storm Dragon,
I, Rimuru Tempest,
will protect you!
I've decided
to grant you your wish.
[gasps]
[ELDER]
Thank you so much, Lord Rimuru.
We are eternally grateful to you
and from this day forward
we are your loyal servants.
You can count on me!
And that's the story
of how I became
the leader of the Goblins,
and their guardian.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time:
"Battle at the Goblin Village."