♪
[RIMURU]
We're headed to the marshlands
to meet with
the Lizardman Chieftain.
Once we're there,
we'll sign the treaty
and help defeat the orc army.
The members of my party include:
Benimaru, Shion, Hakurou,
and Souei, who's out scouting.
-Of course Ranga's here.
-[barks]
[RIMURU]
And our Goblin Riders.
I left Rigurd
and the rest of our gang
to guard the village.
I've instructed them to evacuate
if anything happens to us.
[SOUEI] Lord Rimuru,
do you have a moment?
[RIMURU]
What's up, Souei?
[SOUEI] I've come across
some sort of skirmish.
I believe
it's the personal guard
-to the Lizardman Chieftain.
-[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER grunts]
[SOUEI] She appears to be
fighting a high-ranking orc.
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER grunting]
[SOUEI]
What are your orders?
[RIMURU]
Well, I mean...
It only makes sense
to help her out.
Can you win?
[SOUEI]
Quite easily.
[RIMURU]
So confident!
Being skilled and handsome
seems kinda unfair.
Do it. We'll be there soon.
[SOUEI]
Yes, sir.
[RIMURU]
Assume battle formation.
We're riding to help Souei.
-[ALL] Sir!
-[GOBTA] Let's do it!
Go, Ranga.
[RANGA]
As you command.
[crickets chirping]
[GOBTA]
Uh, Lord Rimuru?
I thought you said
there was a battle.
[BENIMARU] He didn't leave
any fun for us.
[HAKUROU]
Hmm.
[RIMURU]
Oh, man.
Gotta give it to him,
Souei's got some mad skills.
She has been injured.
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER groaning]
On it.
[coughs]
Don't worry. This will help you.
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER
groans, gasps]
What? My wound?
But I was certain
that it was fatal.
Who are you?
I am Rimuru Tempest.
[gasps]
Huh?
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER]
Please, I need your help.
Will you save my father,
the Lizardman Chieftain,
as well as my brother, Gabiru?
They're in grave danger.
Wait, you're Gabiru's sister?
Yes.
[RIMURU]
What happened?
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER]
My brother led a rebellion
and imprisoned
both me and my father.
[gasps]
To make matters worse,
he and his men are attempting
to fight the orc army.
But he... He's underestimated
the Orc Lord.
If we don't act quickly,
then the lizardmen
will be exterminated.
When the guards
weren't looking,
my father helped me escape
so I could warn you.
I know that this is
a selfish request.
Especially after we broke
our promise to wait for you.
But still, a powerful majin
such as yourself
could surely help.
I'll do anything you want.
I'm begging you. Save my people.
Very well spoken.
That you recognize
our lord's power,
speaks of your great potential.
Uh, hold on a minute.
[SHION]
Come on now, stand up.
I'm certain that the lizardmen
can be saved
just as you requested.
[RIMURU]
Say what?
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER]
Thank you so much.
[RIMURU] She just accepted work
on my behalf again.
She really is a secretary.
All right then.
We were gonna fight
the orcs either way.
Let's see. You said you're
the Chieftain's daughter, right?
Uh, yes.
I'm yours to command, my lord.
[RIMURU] Good. Then you'll act
as the Chieftain's proxy.
Do you object to forging
an alliance right here and now?
[gasps]
No. Not at all.
Then it's settled.
Consider us your new allies.
Right. Thank you.
Souei, can you use
Shadow Movement
to get to the Chieftain?
Of course I can.
Man, his skills are legit.
Please go and rescue
the Lizardman Chieftain.
Yes, sir.
You have my gratitude.
Everyone else,
continue the march.
[ALL]
Sir!
♪
-[ORCS yelling]
-[metal clanging]
[ORCS]
Trample all. Trample all.
Trample all.
I told you these orcs
were no match for the lizardmen.
Right! Withdraw for now.
Our plan was to toy with them,
and then have the goblins
we recruited finish them off.
But at the rate we're going,
we won't even need
the extra help.
[LIZARDMAN screams]
[GABIRU]
What's happening?
The orcs are eating
other orcs?
[shudders]
[ORC grunts]
[screaming]
Oh, please no! Somebody help me!
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[LIZARDMAN SOLDIER]
Sir... Sir Gabiru!
[screaming]
All units, fall back, now!
Full retreat!
[gasps] Sir Gabiru.
They've already surrounded us.
But how?
[GABIRU]
What just happened?
It's like the orcs are suddenly
capable of moving quicker.
[GABIRU gasps]
Impossible! Webbed feet
and scales on an orc?
But that would mean they have
the same abilities we do.
They just ate
one of our men, sir.
It's true.
And that's when
the enemy started moving faster.
[GABIRU]
Ugh!
So they ate a lizardman
and gained our powers?
[GABIRU grunting]
[GABIRU grunts]
Listen up, everyone.
Stand close together!
Keep the goblins in the center.
Leave no openings!
We must shield the goblins
while breaking through
the orc army's formation.
[LIZARDMEN yelling]
[GABIRU] If it was just us,
perhaps we could have escaped.
Bringing the goblins
into this fight
worked against us in the end.
[ORCS]
Trample all. Trample all.
Our allies' powers
will become our own.
The enemies' powers
Don't be afraid.
Show them the strength and power
on which we lizardmen
pride ourselves!
-[ORCS] Trample all.
-[LIZARDMEN yelling]
[gasps]
[LIZARDMEN gasping]
What?
This Orc's aura,
it's incredible.
[grunting]
You who stand before me,
you must be
the Orc Lord, correct?
I am the great chieftain
of the lizardmen, Gabiru!
I challenge you
to a one-on-one--
[ORC GENERAL]
I am not the Lord.
I am just an Orc General.
Compared to the Orc Lord,
my power is quite inferior.
Wait, you're seriously
just a general?
Even with an aura
that overwhelming,
he's still considered inferior?
[ORC GENERAL]
You wish to fight one-on-one?
Interesting.
I'll oblige you.
I thank you.
Still, I can't help but wonder
about the Orc Lord,
and what kind of monster
he must be.
[LAPLACE]
Yes!
Goodie good good!
It's going splendidly,
wouldn't you agree, Lord Gelmud?
[GELMUD]
Indeed.
[LAPLACE] Looks like everything
is unfolding just as we planned.
[LAPLACE chuckling]
[GELMUD]
It won't be long until my child
gains complete control
over the forest.
And then my ambitions
will finally--
[TREYNI]
Well, you two seem to be having
quite the little party.
[LAPLACE]
Who's there?
I am the dryad, Treyni.
And you are trespassers
in my forest.
[LAPLACE] This puts a kink
in our plan, Lord Gelmud.
Dryads are the caretakers here.
[GELMUD]
Are you serious?
For the disruption
you've both caused,
I'm removing you
from these woods.
[GELMUD]
What?
Now, Spirit Summoning. Sylphide!
[LAPLACE]
Whoa, hold on a second.
Can't we talk about this?
I will pass judgment.
Pray in repentance
for your sins.
Aerial Blade, go!
[ethereal vocalizing]
[GELMUD grunting]
[GELMUD]
Hey! Laplace, your arm.
[LAPLACE] Come on, lady,
you're being irrational.
Looks like talking is out.
Not that it matters
since we've achieved our goal.
I guess this means
the party's over.
See you later.
♪
They've escaped me.
This is not a desirable outcome.
Rimuru Tempest.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Defeat the Orc Lord.
♪
[GABIRU groaning]
[grunting]
[yelling]
Vortex Crash!
[grunts]
[grunting]
Chaos Eater!
♪
[grunts]
[GABIRU]
You're trying to eat me?
[ORC GENERAL laughs menacingly]
[ORC GENERAL] Do you think
you can run forever?
-Sir Gabiru!
-We'll help you!
[GABIRU]
Stay out of this.
[LIZARDMEN gasp]
I'll handle it myself.
[ALL gasp]
That's our leader! Gabiru!
[cries]
Gabiru!
[LIZARDMEN cheering]
Gabiru! Gabiru!
Gabiru!
[GABIRU grunts]
[LIZARDMEN]
Gabiru!
[ORC GENERAL grunting]
[GABIRU grunting]
[ALL gasping]
This is nothing.
[yelling]
[ORC GENERAL]
What?
[ALL gasp]
[GABIRU yells]
[GABIRU grunting]
[groaning]
Sir Gabiru!
[GABIRU groaning weakly]
[heavy footsteps]
[gasps]
Looks like you'll die
crawling on the ground
as a lizard should.
Say goodbye!
-[ALL scream]
-[GABIRU shudders]
[ORC GENERAL grunts]
[GABIRU gasps]
[GABIRU]
It's you.
The guy who's the true leader
of that weird goblin village.
Huh?
[GOBTA] Did he take
too many whacks to the head?
[GABIRU] Hold on, did you
come here to save all of us?
[RANGA]
That's Gobta.
He is the captain
of the Goblin Riders.
You're that direwolf.
[RANGA]
My name is Ranga.
My master, Rimuru,
told me to come help you.
But how did you get here
so quickly?
[RANGA] Shadow Movement.
Try to pay attention.
[ORC GENERAL laughs]
[ORC GENERAL]
Rimuru, you say?
I don't know
who any of you newcomers are,
but if you stand in my way,
I'll show you no mercy!
♪
[explosions]
[ORCS yelling]
Oh, nice!
Heh. Looks like it's starting!
[ORC GENERAL]
Huh.
Is this magic
from the lizardmen?
The time
for playing around is over.
I have to find whoever is using
that magic and end them!
♪
[grunting]
So, uh, Gabiru or whatever
your name is,
we should probably assume
a defensive formation.
[GABIRU gasps]
Right, I understand,
but still...
-[GOBTA gasps]
-[explosions]
[GABIRU]
What's causing those flames?
[GOBTA]
Oh, no need to worry.
They're definitely on our side.
[ORCS screaming]
[GOBTA]
I think.
[BENIMARU]
This is why I told you to move.
[ORC]
Who... Who are you?
What do you want?
You've forgotten us? How rude.
And after you went
and devoured our whole village.
[scoffs]
Those horns. Are you ogres?
Us? No.
Perhaps that's why
you can't remember us.
The time has come.
Yes, and, we should
thank Lord Rimuru
for this opportunity.
I'll say it once more,
you'd best move out of our way.
Unless, of course, you'd prefer
to die an agonizing death.
[ORC]
Hmm?
[grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[explosion]
[ORCS screaming]
Amazing.
[ORC GENERAL scoffs]
[ORC GENERAL] It appears you've
come to assist the lizards.
How foolish.
Goblins and dogs?
A pathetic rescue team.
As if any of you weaklings
could ever possibly
defeat a superior
monster such as myself.
Pathetic?
[RANGA]
All right. We'll show you.
[growling]
♪
Huh?
[gasping]
[RIMURU]
What the what?!
♪
[screaming]
[RIMURU]
Are those tornadoes?
[GREAT SAGE] Answer, this is
the wide-range attack
of the individual Ranga,
Death Storm.
[RIMURU]
Oh. Sweet.
[groaning]
[ORC GENERAL]
Curse you!
[screaming]
-[groaning]
-[RANGA howling]
[GOBTA groans]
Hmm?
No way!
Ranga turned into
a Tempest Star Wolf.
[RANGA]
Do you see now, filthy orcs?
This is a fraction
of the power
wielded by someone you mocked
as being pathetic.
[GOBTA]
There's nobody there.
[RANGA]
Exactly!
♪
This battle will mark
a brand-new beginning for us.
[sword slashing]
[ORCS screaming]
Lord Rimuru will inevitably be
the winner of many conflicts.
But this is the first step
on his path. You see?
[ORCS grunting]
[ORC SOLDIER]
Enough talk, get her!
[yelling]
[SHION]
Hmm.
[grunts]
[ORCS screaming]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[SHION]
Did you see me?
[RIMURU]
Uh, yep.
[chuckles]
[RIMURU]
Remind me to never piss her off.
More importantly,
what used to be a sizable
orc army is now shrinking.
Those Kijin really know
how to bring the pain.
Man, I really hope
they'll decide to hang around
after the war is over.
I wonder how things
are going for Souei.
-[sword slashing]
-[ORCS screaming]
[LIZARDMAN groaning]
[LIZARDMAN]
We're alive?
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER hissing]
-Here, give him this.
-Huh?
[keys jangling]
[door opens]
[CHIEFTAIN]
Huh?
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER]
Father!
[CHIEFTAIN gasps]
[CHIEFTAIN chuckles]
You came to rescue us?
Thank you, Souei.
I don't understand.
[SOUEI]
We have formed an alliance.
But how? I was here.
Well, I formed it
on your behalf, Father,
as your representative.
Reinforcements are coming.
Is that true?
Yes, there was light
at the end of the tunnel.
You were right.
[CHIEFTAIN]
Our people are saved.
How wonderful.
[ORC laughing]
[CHIEFTAIN gasps]
[grunting]
Souei, no!
[SOUEI]
No need to worry.
I've already immobilized him.
[groaning]
[gasping]
It seems Souei has
that effect on everyone.
[CHIEFTAIN]
Then, I was right.
Forming an alliance
with these people
was the correct choice.
[ORC groaning]
This message is for
the orcs' puppet master.
You are next.
Destroying the ogres' village,
and making enemies of the Kijin
will be the greatest
of your regrets.
[groaning]
[ORC roaring]
[LIZARDMEN gasping]
♪
[GELMUD]
Damn them all!
Stupid, useless orcs!
And the Kijin?
I do remember having
Geld attack an ogre village.
Does this mean
the survivors from there
somehow evolved?
Not to mention
the wolf creature.
No one said there was a beast
like that in the Forest of Jura.
There are far too many
unknown variables
in this equation
that I've somehow missed.
This is terrible.
I must do something,
or risk my plan falling apart
after I've come so far.
If this continues,
then I will most certainly
be put to death by him.
♪
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
Hey, guys.
I found the Orc Lord.
[BENIMARU]
Right.
[ORC LORD]
I'm so hungry!
I want to eat something.
Anything!
[RIMURU]
Orc Lord.
I'm going to end you.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"The One Who Devours All."