[RIMURU] Shizu had
one last regret before she died.
And it was that she wasn't able
to help children
who had been summoned
to this world
in an incomplete form.
So she entrusted them
to Rimuru.
Their bodies,
which were still maturing,
were unable to control
the immense
magicule energy within them.
As a result, that energy
would eventually go berserk,
destroying their bodies
and ultimately
dooming them to die.
Rimuru believed Shizu
was able to survive
so long after her summoning
because the spirit, Ifrit,
possessed her body
right after her arrival,
which allowed her to
ultimately control her energy.
In order to save the children,
Rimuru set out
to find superior spirits
to inhabit their bodies.
Shizu, I swear that I'm gonna
save these kids.
[RIMURU]
This is probably the entrance.
The Dwelling of Spirits should
be just beyond these doors.
Are you guys ready for this?
Once we enter,
we may never leave.
[KIDS whimper]
Of course we're ready.
-Yeah.
-Right, let's do this.
Plus, it's gonna take
more than that to scare us.
[CHLOE groans]
Hmm.
[RIMURU laughs softly]
Hey. If this goes south,
take care of them.
[RANGA] Your students
are my students, master.
Fear not, I will protect them
with my life.
Thanks.
Let's go.
♪
[KENYA]
It's just a straight path.
[ALICE]
What gives?
I thought this was supposed
to be a labyrinth or whatever.
[RYOTA]
I don't know.
Something seems off about it.
[CHLOE whimpers]
Make sure you all
stick together.
[ALL]
Uh, yes, sir.
[RIMURU]
It may look straight,
but there are traps meant to
confuse your sense of direction
set all over the place.
With human senses alone,
it's possible
that we could end up
unable to move forward
or go back.
It's a good thing
I have my mental map.
-[FEMALE VOICE giggles]
-[RIMURU gasps]
[KIDS groan]
[VOICE chuckling]
-[VOICE laughing]
-[FAIRIES giggling]
What are those voices?
They're everywhere.
It sounds like they're
resonating inside of our minds.
[RIMURU] Could it be
thought transference?
Or telepathy maybe?
[VOICE]
Come on, that's not any fun.
Isn't this scary?
You should be more afraid.
[laughing and giggling
continues]
[CHLOE whimpers]
[VOICE]
There you go.
It's a lot more entertaining
if you show your fear.
Are you one of the spirits
that hangs out here?
I need to have words
with a superior spirit.
You think you could possibly
take us to one
without getting in our way?
[VOICE laughing]
[VOICE]
What an amusing request.
Okay, of course I'll show you.
[RIMURU]
Sweet, that was easy.
[VOICE]
Not so fast.
First things first.
[RIMURU]
What's that mean?
[CHLOE groans]
-There. Look, Teach.
-[RIMURU gasps]
♪
[energy surges]
[RIMURU]
Oh, look, it's an ominous path.
I guess we should follow it.
-[VOICE chuckling]
-[FAIRIES giggling]
♪
[RIMURU]
It's a dead end.
[VOICE]
There's no rush, no rush.
Behold, "Small World."
[RIMURU gasps]
[VOICE laughs]
Well?
What do you think?
So awesome.
[VOICE]
Now, it's time for a test.
♪
[RIMURU]
Yeah, that's not a good sign.
A glowing red eye
is always a giveaway
that you're dealing
with an evil dude.
Hey. Is the test
just beating the tin can?
[VOICE]
Ding-ding-ding. That's correct.
[FAIRIES giggling]
[RIMURU]
For real?
Talk about easy.
-[RANGA] Shall I destroy it?
-[RIMURU] Mm-mmm.
[RIMURU]
Focus on protecting the kids.
If something happens to me,
then get them out of here.
[RANGA]
Right.
Um, Teach?
It'll be fine.
He's super swol, remember?
[VOICE] What's this?
What's this? What's this?
Taking it on alone?
Your overconfidence
might be your downfall.
♪
[RIMURU]
Great Sage, use Appraisal.
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
This is a Golem with a body
made from magisteel.
[RIMURU]
Ugh. Damn, that's insane.
Its magicule count
is off the charts.
It's even stronger
than that stupid Sky Dragon.
What to do?
It probably weighs a ton.
[grunts]
What the actual hell?!
It's trying to kill me!
How is this a "test"?!
[VOICE]
Better be careful.
If you let your guard down,
you could die.
Think you can win?
Do you? Do you?
[RIMURU] She talks about death
so casually.
It's definitely fast,
but I think I can evade it.
The real question is,
how do I beat it?
Since it's made of metal,
Black Thunder is probably out.
The electric shock would just
run through the ground
and fry us.
My sword won't do much, either.
What should I do?
[CHLOE]
Be careful!
[RIMURU]
It's okay.
I've got the entire situation
on lock down.
♪
[RIMURU]
Listen, if you apologize now,
then I'll let you off the hook.
But if you don't, then,
I'll be forced to
recycle your friend, here.
[VOICE laughing]
[FAIRIES giggling]
[VOICE]
How interesting.
You're more than welcome to try.
Do it, do it.
[RIMURU grunts]
Arcane Thread Fetters.
[VOICE]
What?
You tied up
my Elemental Colossus?
You'd better say goodbye
to your toy robot.
[VOICE]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
[RIMURU]
Hell Flare!
[ALL chuckle]
Wow. That's incredible.
[ALICE] I mean, I guess
it's pretty cool.
For a teacher.
[VOICE]
Impossible!
No way!
With just one hit?!
[explosion]
Boom.
That's how it's done.
You're the coolest, Teach!
-[CHLOE] Uh-huh!
-For real.
You might even be stronger
than Miss Shizu was.
[ALICE] Beating that was
the least he could do.
Oh, come on, it's not
like you could do it.
[KIDS laughing]
Now, then,
if you don't wanna join
your tin friend,
then you better show yourself.
I know where you're hiding,
so just give up, already.
[VOICE shrieks]
Okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay!
[RIMURU gasps]
I'm here, so just hold
your stupid fire!
This thing has been
humiliating enough.
[GALE]
A fairy?
[CHLOE]
She's cute.
Who are you?
Ta-da!
Behold, I'm one of the Ten...
[CHLOE]
The poor thing bit her tongue.
I bet it's because she usually
speaks using telepathy.
You okay?
[FAIRY]
I'm fine, I'm fine.
As I was saying, I'm one of
the Ten Great Demon Lords.
Ramiris of the Labyrinth,
at your service.
-[KENYA] Uh...
-What now?
Know your place.
Grovel at my tiny feet.
[RAMIRIS groans]
[RAMIRIS]
Just what the heck was that?!
-A chop?
-[RAMIRIS] Obviously!
[RIMURU] There's no way
you can be what you say you are.
If you're gonna lie,
at least make it believable.
A pipsqueak like you
is a far cry
from a real Demon Lord.
[RAMIRIS] Why, you... How dare
you call me a pipsqueak?
I am a Demon Lord,
what else would I be?!
-An idiot?
-I'm not an idiot!
A nice jerk?
Yes, exactly, I'm a nice jerk.
Hey!
Putting "nice" in front of it
doesn't make it less mean!
[RIMURU]
Hmm...
I don't know, my friend Milim
is a real Demon Lord.
And when I compare
the two of you,
you definitely seem weaker.
[grunts sharply]
Dummy!
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy,
dummy, dummy, you big dummy!
[RAMIRIS panting]
Now you listen to me.
The rest of us call Milim
the Demon Lord of Absurdity.
She just skips around punching
anyone who gets in her way.
How dare you compare me,
a beautiful, delicate flower,
to that overly violent,
pink-haired tornado?!
You'd better tone down
the attitude, mister,
or we'll have big problems!
Huge problems! Giant problems!
[RIMURU]
Damn, she's obnoxious.
On the subject
of "overly violent,"
you, sir, have no business
using dangerous moves like that.
You shouldn't be so reckless.
Is it true
that you really know Milim?
Yeah, we met recently.
[RAMIRIS]
Hmm...
Hold on a second.
Could it be that you're
that slime monster
who became the new leader
of the Great Forest of Jura?
[RIMURU] That's me.
I'm impressed you know.
[RAMIRIS]
Wow, that's incredible!
[KENYA]
Wait.
[ALICE]
You're a slime?
[RIMURU]
Yep.
Holy cow, it's true!
No way.
[RIMURU]
Surprise!
Adorable.
Sorry I didn't tell you guys.
[KENYA]
Awesome!
[RYOTA] You're like
the strongest slime ever.
[ALICE]
It's not that big of a deal.
[GALE] You truly are
a master of surprise, sir.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, it's a thing.
I'll tell you about it sometime.
Hello. Did you guys forget
that I was here?!
Oh, sorry.
Anyway, how exactly
did you hear about me?
You know how Milim is, right?
She showed up for
the first time in ages,
bragging about her
"bestie for restie,"
I thought she was lying
but I guess I was wrong.
[RIMURU]
If Milim really was here,
then that could mean
this fairy is telling the truth
about the whole
Demon Lord thing.
Why do you still look
suspicious of me?
You'd better believe that
I'm a real Demon Lord.
[RIMURU]
It's like she can read minds.
[FAIRIES giggling]
[mouthful]
It's so tasty. Wow!
Tasty, tasty, tasty.
[RIMURU] That cookie
is bigger than she is,
where does she put it?
[RAMIRIS]
Just so you know,
I never intended to actually
kill you or anything.
Seriously?
[RAMIRIS]
Seriously.
I was just gonna toy
with you a bit,
and then rush in
and save you at the last minute
to win your undying respect.
That's terrible.
It was the perfect plan.
But then you vaporized
my poor Elemental Colossus.
I spent all that time tinkering
with it to get it working,
and now it's just gone.
Don't blame me.
I thought it was either kill
or be killed, you know?
You don't get it.
That Colossus was
extra sophisticated.
[RIMURU]
Uh...
[RAMIRIS] I used earth spirits
to control its weight,
water spirits
to move its joints,
fire spirits
to generate power,
and wind spirits
to regulate heat.
It was a work of art.
That machine was the best
in spirit engineering.
Spirit engineering?
That sounds familiar.
[KAIJIN]
One of the projects
that Vesta had been
under pressure to complete,
the Magisoldier Project,
went up in smoke.
Is that like
the Magisoldier project
the dwarves and elves
were working on together?
The ones from Dwargon?
Ding, ding, ding, ding.
Yes, that's correct.
The whole reason
that project failed
is because they couldn't
produce the magicore
to act as the unit's heart.
There's also the fact
that plain ol' boring steel
would never be able to withstand
the full power of a spirit.
After it went berserk
and fell apart,
they threw out its shell.
So I bought it here
and restored it.
That's genius-level stuff.
I'm amazing, aren't I?
[RIMURU]
I guess.
It is pretty amazing, though.
I mean, she did manage
to complete the research
that Vesta's team failed at.
She comes off as an idiot.
But this Demon Lord Ramiris
is actually pretty smart.
All right, I'll admit
you're amazing.
[RAMIRIS]
Hmm?
So I have a big favor to ask
based on that fact.
Oh, a favor, huh?
Well, you can forget about it,
you're not the boss of me.
Never mind.
After all, it can't hurt
to at least hear you out, right?
I'm glad you're so open-minded.
[RAMIRIS sighs]
-I'm willing to pay, of course.
-[RAMIRIS] Huh?
If you agree to help me out,
then I can whip up
a shiny new Golem
for you, no problemo.
Well, start talkin'.
♪
[RIMURU] I explained everything
about the children to her,
including the part
about their looming deaths.
And how we needed
superior spirits
to help the kids get control
of their magicules.
Which is why we had come
to the labyrinth.
[RAMIRIS mouthful]
Oh, I get it now.
Those children have it
pretty rough, huh?
Yep.
And so, I was hoping that maybe
you could introduce me
to the Queen of the Spirits.
[RAMIRIS]
Hmm?
I see.
Guess I should tell you, then.
-I'm the queen.
-[RIMURU gasps]
Come on. Try to keep up.
I said I'm the queen.
[RIMURU]
Uh...
Hey, that's not very funny.
[blows a raspberry]
I'm telling the truth!
It's not a joke!
But that's crazy.
How can a Demon Lord become
the Queen of the Spirits, huh?
No!
You've got it backwards.
Yeah?
I was the Queen of the Spirits,
but I fell from grace
and became a Demon Lord.
That kind of sounds
unbelievable.
[RAMIRIS] I don't know
what to tell you, it's true.
It's easy, you know,
to fall from grace.
Come to think of it,
that guy fell from grace, too.
What guy?
-Oh, Leon.
-[RIMURU gasps]
[RAMIRIS]
He came here on a mission
because he was trying
to find some answers.
So he called on
a superior spirit, and, shabam.
They made a contract.
Boy, was I surprised.
Once he managed that,
I had no choice
but to recognize him as a Hero
and grant him protection
as the Queen of the Spirits,
'cause that's all in
my job description, you know?
[RIMURU]
Hang on!
How did a guy who used to be
a Hero become a Demon Lord?
[RAMIRIS]
Like I said, he fell from grace.
He was probably copying me.
You're saying
you have to fall from grace
to become a Demon Lord?
[RAMIRIS] Yeah. But I could
still take that little punk.
Easy-peasy.
One punch, he's out.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, I'm sure.
It's so weird.
I never thought a Hero
could become a Demon Lord.
[RAMIRIS]
Know what else?
That Leon said something
pretty outrageous.
He wanted to summon
someone specific
from another world.
[RIMURU]
Really?
[RAMIRIS]
As if that's even possible.
What a moron.
He looked like he was gonna cry.
No, he did cry.
It's not a stretch
to say he cried.
What a demanding cry baby.
I'd take him out with one punch,
I tell ya!
[RAMIRIS grunting]
[RIMURU]
Hmm. That's interesting.
It sounds like
this Demon Lord Leon dude
might be even more formidable
than I had originally thought.
Maybe Ramiris should chill out.
Who knows what Leon would do
if he found out she was
talking smack about him?
Heck, I'm pretty sure I could
take her out so I know he could.
Hey, you're thinking something
really rude
right now, aren't you?
Nope, not at all.
So are you planning on taking me
to the Dwelling of Spirits
or not?
♪
[RAMIRIS] You know,
I'm not just a Demon Lord.
I'm also the
Guide of Saints,
and the Fairy
of the Labyrinth,
as well as the former
Queen of Spirits.
Just like with Leon,
it's my duty to bestow
my divine protection
upon any traveling Heroes
I may meet.
I promise there's nothing
you need to worry about,
because I'm an impartial party.
You see, it's my job.
I'm here to maintain
the balance of this world.
[FAIRIES giggling]
♪
Now, come.
I will aid you
in your summoning.
Hopefully you'll call
powerful spirits.
[footsteps]
[RAMIRIS]
Treyni?
Wow, it's great to hear
those girls are doing so well.
They were such cute
little spirits back in the day.
That's weird.
Treyni said that she had
no connection
with the current
Queen of the Spirits.
[RAMIRIS]
Ah, of course.
Even after dying
and being reborn,
I've retained my memories
from my previous life.
To be fair, they probably
don't know that, though.
I haven't seen them since we got
split up a long time ago.
You should tell them to come
and visit me sometime.
[GIRLS giggle]
[RIMURU]
Will do.
[RAMIRIS]
I can't wait.
[KIDS gasp]
[RIMURU]
What is this?
[RAMIRIS] The deepest part
of the Labyrinth,
the Dwelling of Spirits.
[RIMURU]
Feels a lot like Veldora's cave.
It's overflowing
with natural energy.
Will we be able
to find spirits here?
[RAMIRIS]
Yes, but remember that they have
wills of their own.
They'll only answer your summons
if they feel like it.
Okay, so what happens
if they don't show up?
You could always siphon off
some of their energy
and create
a new superior spirit.
For real?
You're saying if they won't
respond to our summons,
we could essentially just make
a new spirit altogether?
[RAMIRIS]
Right.
[RIMURU]
This won't be easy.
I'm concerned
about their affinities.
But what other choice
do we have?
Plus, we've got
my Unique Skill, Degenerate,
which specializes
in unification and separation.
If Demon Lord Leon can do it,
then so can I.
Ready?
[KENYA]
Mm-hmm.
We can handle it.
Let's go.
Uh, yeah, I'm not scared
or anything.
Ready when you are.
[RANGA barks]
That's the spirit.
Right.
Kenya, Ryota, Chloe,
Alice, and Gale.
-Game time.
-[KIDS] Yeah!
[RAMIRIS chuckles]
♪
[RIMURU] Shizu, I hope
that you can somehow see this.
[KIDS giggling]
[RIMURU]
I promise you,
I will fulfill your final wish.
♪
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time, "Saved Souls."