[VERYARD] So, you're telling me
that a mere slime
managed to beat the Orc Lord?
And it built a city?
That's all rather
hard to believe.
A tall tale, at best.
And yet, I know that it isn't.
It's strange, but I suppose
we might owe our lives
to a slime named Rimuru.
Yes, true.
So, what sort of relationship
should we seek
with this monster town?
Should we work off
of the assumption
that the slime
is a benevolent creature?
Or treat it like a threat
and attempt to eliminate it?
You forget that "attempt"
is the key word here.
Would it even be possible?
Are you looking
for an honest answer?
I doubt I actually need
to hear it.
[FUZE sighs]
Okay, I'll go check it out.
I think it's time I met
this Rimuru face-to-face.
All right, let's move out.
I can't wait to see this slime
you've told me about.
[ALL sigh]
[MILIM blowing air]
Mm!
It's delicious!
I can't believe how much
amazing food you have here.
Can I have seconds?
♪
[RIMURU]
How ya holdin' up, pal?
I'm perfectly fine.
Strong as... [groans]
[strained speech] ...a rock or
something else indestructible.
That's our Sir Gabiru for you.
[RIMURU]
Is the communication crystal
working okay?
Yes.
We can now contact King Gazel.
I let him know
about the situation
with the Demon Lord Milim
and how well you handled it.
[RIMURU]
Word.
In the mean time, we'll just
have to keep a close eye on her.
I'll leave the reporting
up to you.
Right.
This is one of
Lord Rimuru's potions.
Ninety-nine percent
of its composition
is extracted
from hipokute herbs.
You can drink it down or apply
it directly to the wound.
For instant recovery!
Behold, the Full Potion!
[RIMURU]
Mm-hmm.
To contrast that,
dwarven techniques
only allow us to create potions
with a 98 percent
healing effect.
The potions we make
are known as "high potions."
A mere one percent
may seem small,
but it makes a big difference
when it comes to potency.
After all this time,
I've finally overcome
that one percent barrier.
And this is the result
of those efforts.
[RIMURU]
Cool.
I'll do a quick appraisal.
[VESTA]
I would be honored.
[RIMURU] Great Sage,
please use Appraisal.
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
This potion is equal
to that of a Full Potion.
[RIMURU]
Good news, my dude.
It's definitely a Full Potion.
Wow, excellent work, Vesta!
I'm so glad I could assist you
in this endeavor.
You should be
proud of yourself.
See? I knew you were
the perfect man
to conduct this research.
Kaijin, thank you.
[KAIJIN laughs]
[RIMURU] Oof. I can't believe
he actually pulled it off.
I wonder if we could
mass produce it.
I think if we sold this,
it'd be a great way
to bring money into Tempest.
Uh...
Hmm.
[KAIJIN] I'm not sure
it'll be that simple.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
The Full Potion might be
a little too effective.
We shouldn't rely on it
for everyday use.
Quality potions like these
should be reserved
for high-level champions
in life or death situations.
Yes, I agree.
The potions we sell
in the Dwarven Kingdom
are low potions
which have been mass-produced
by diluting high potions.
[RIMURU]
Huh.
This is a great opportunity.
We could talk to King Gazel
and see if he'll let us
make those potions here.
Hey, now there's a smart idea.
If we produce and sell
the potions here...
Yeah, it could work.
We'd just need to get
the ingredients
from the Dwarven Kingdom.
[RIMURU]
I get it.
And then both nations
reap the reward.
Sweet.
Let's start the negotiations.
I'll leave the rest
of the production details
up to you guys.
[VESTA and KAIJIN]
Right.
[BOTH gasp]
[wind rushing]
[gasps]
[indistinct chatter]
Okay, what happened?
Our town just received
a new visitor.
However, Lady Milim did not
take kindly to him.
[RIMURU]
Let me through.
[groaning]
Rigurd, everything okay?
[RIGURD]
Lord Rimuru, it's you.
-[RIMURU gasps]
-Do not worry.
For this is nothing
more than a mere scratch.
[RIMURU]
Like hell it is!
Is that who hurt you?
Yes, sir.
-[MILIM] Oh, Rimuru!
-[RIMURU groans]
This guy thought
he could come stir up trouble.
So I taught him a lesson
using my fist.
I'm one of Demon Lord Carrion's
Three Beastketeers.
Phobio the Black Leopard Fang.
Of all our master's
Beastketeers,
I'm the strongest one.
Nice town you got here.
Fit to be ruled by
the Beast King, don't you think?
How about it, grandpa?
Surely you jest.
[groaning]
[CROWD gasps]
[low rumbling]
Hmm?
♪
[grunting]
[gasps]
It's Demon Lord Milim!
[grunts]
Leopard Fang Flaming Palm!
Stupid jerk!
That was
my bestie's subordinate!
[chuckles]
[RIMURU] Does she think
I'm gonna praise her?
[chuckles softly]
[RIMURU]
Better question,
should I encourage
this behavior?
[chuckles softly]
[RIMURU] No doubt
there'll be ramifications
for laying out one of Demon Lord
Carrion's Beastke-whatevers.
[sighs]
Didn't you promise me you'd be
on your best behavior?
Huh?
Well, yeah, that is true.
But this is way different.
He's not from your town
so it totally doesn't count.
It's good, it's all good!
-[RIMURU] No, it's bad.
-[MILIM gasps]
Though, I suppose you at least
defended Rigurd's honor,
so I'll only take
your lunch away.
You meanie.
I was only helping!
[MILIM grunts]
This is your fault,
you stupid piece of crap!
I'll make you pay.
I've already lost my lunch today
so I might as well
punch you some more.
[RIMURU]
No, no, no!
♪
[chewing happily]
[RIMURU]
So, why did you come here again?
[scoffs]
As if I owe any answers
to a lowly slime like you.
[ALL]
Hmm!
[RIMURU]
Doesn't matter what you call me,
I'm still way stronger
than you, brah.
I don't know
Demon Lord Carrion,
but depending on
how you behave,
my people could become
your master's enemies.
Do you really wanna
be responsible
for pissing off the entire
Great Forest of Jura?
Please. That's some big talk.
There's no way a slime is
the boss of this pitiful town.
But I guess that explains
the weak followers.
Lady Milim hanging around here
must have given you a fat head.
Watch it, jerk.
I don't take kindly to people
insulting my bestie.
[PHOBIO gasps]
[RIMURU]
Stand down, Milim.
Any more punches and you can
kiss your dinner goodbye.
[MILIM whimpers]
Yeah, okay.
I promise to be good.
[RIMURU]
Now, it's true that I'm a slime.
But it's also true
that I rule 30 percent
of the Great Forest of Jura.
If you don't want me
to declare war,
you'd better start
singing a different tune.
So, I'll ask again,
why did you come here?
Ugh.
We came to this dumb town
on Lord Carrion's orders.
He wants all the majin here
to serve him.
[RIMURU]
Ah.
He must mean us.
I should have guessed that Milim
wouldn't be the only Demon Lord
spying on that battle
with the Orc Lord.
[MILIM]
Damn that Carrion.
He broke his promise to me.
[MILIM grunting]
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[MILIM sighs innocently]
[sighs]
[RIMURU]
Cool, I've heard enough.
-You're free to go.
-[PHOBIO] Huh?
Are you sure?
But he attacked us.
[RIMURU] Come on,
I'm not gonna off the guy.
Give Demon Lord Carrion
a message.
Tell him that
if he wants to talk,
then he can choose a date
and we'll speak with him
at that time.
[grunts]
You'll regret making
a fool out of me.
[RIMURU]
Somehow I doubt
he's going to deliver
that message.
Okay. What's the scoop
with this Demon Lord Carrion?
I'm sorry, but I can't
tell you anything.
We've sworn not to interfere
with each other's plans.
[RIMURU]
And yet she just admitted
that there is some kinda secret.
Oh, did you only make
that promise with Carrion?
Or does it maybe involve
other Demon Lords as well?
Well, yeah. Uh, maybe.
Come on, it's okay.
After all, Carrion sent some
underling to interfere with you.
Huh?
[RIMURU]
And we're besties,
so we can tell each other
anything, right?
So, I'm sure it would be
okay for you
to tell me about some of
the other Demon Lords you know.
[MILIM whimpering]
Plus, if I don't know what kind
of promise you made to them,
I may accidentally interfere
without realizing it.
Yeah, I guess.
But still, I promised them.
[RIMURU]
I know.
We should make you
a special weapon.
As your best friend,
your well-being is my priority.
A special weapon?
[laughs]
You've got a point.
There's nothing more important
than your best friend's safety.
[RIMURU]
She took it.
Hook, line, and sinker.
I see.
The Demon Lords
Clayman, Carrion, and Frey
used Gelmud in a scheme
to create a puppet Demon Lord,
and you helped.
It seemed like a good way
to kill some time.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, that's one way to put it.
But since we took him down,
it looks like we've become
their new target.
The other Demon Lords are likely
to get involved, too.
What a predicament.
Perhaps we should consult
with Lady Treyni.
Nah, it'll be fine.
Lord Rimuru has nothing to fear
from any of those Demon Lords.
Well, Rimuru,
I told you the big secret.
So when do I get
the special weapon
that you promised me?
Better be soon!
[chuckles]
[RIMURU]
The whirlwind that blew in
with Demon Lord Milim's attack
would continue to gain strength,
eventually threatening to
swallow Rimuru's people whole.
One of the nations surrounding
the Great Forest of Jura
is the Kingdom of Falmuth.
It's a major trade power
known as the gateway
to the Western Provinces.
That same kingdom
had deployed a scouting team
to learn more
about the rumored Orc Lord.
The team was led by
a man named Youm.
They were rowdy,
but their common love of money
kept the team together.
[YOUM]
Hmm.
[rumbling]
-What's wrong?
-Shh.
♪
[GIDO]
Whoa! This is so bad!
[EREN]
Run away!
[KAVAL] Hey, I'll give
the orders around here!
[FUZE] How the hell have you
three stayed alive
this long
when you're so careless?
[YOUM] Some adventurers
have encountered a monster.
[KAJIR]
So what's the plan, boss?
[screams]
[GIDO]
Hey! Wait for us, Eren!
[explosion]
[YOUM]
Hmm?
[EREN]
Oh, hi, excuse us.
[KAVAL]
How about some help?
[GIDO]
Sorry.
[YOUM]
Get ready.
♪
-[ROMMEL gasps]
-A knight spider?
On guard, men. Here we go.
Remove and heal
anyone who gets hurt.
All right. Nobody die.
[ALL]
Sir!
Kajir, take command.
Yes, sir.
[YOUM] Rommel, give me
a strengthening spell.
[energy humming]
As for you,
you'll pay
for getting us involved.
And our services
don't come cheap.
[grunting]
[GOBTA]
No way! Is that you, Kaval?
[KAVAL]
Huh?
Whoa. It is!
-It's Gobta.
-[YOUM] Huh?
Every time I see you,
you're running from something.
You guys sure have
a nose for trouble.
I'll handle the spider.
Dinner's about to be served!
What just happened?
These spiders
are seriously yummy.
-[YOUM] Hmm.
-[FUZE sighs]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[laughter]
Hey, it's almost ready!
I am so hungry!
Hello, I'm Rimuru Tempest,
the representative of this town.
Our nation is called
the Jura Tempest Federation.
Wow, you really are a slime.
By the way, I've gotta ask.
Looks like there are
some new people here,
but who are they?
[RIMURU]
Oh.
This is Benimaru and Shion.
And that's Souei and Shuna.
[MILIM chuckling softly]
[RIMURU]
And that's Milim.
[FUZE gasps]
[MILIM humming softly]
[RIMURU]
Anyway, back to business.
The kingdoms
of Blumund and Falmuth
both came here
to investigate our city?
-Yes, that's right.
-Whoa, hold on.
Why the heck is a slime
acting like a total big shot?
It's crazy.
What's the deal?
Why do you chumps listen to it?
You'd dare insult our master?
-Yeah, I do, ogre tits.
-[RIMURU yells]
[groans]
You okay?!
[RIMURU]
Shion.
Ah! Sorry.
[energy humming]
[RIMURU]
I apologize for Shion's actions.
She's not
the most patient person.
Cut her some slack, okay?
That's not true.
If anything, my patience
is my finest quality.
[laughs]
Wow, you sure have a funny way
of showing patience, Shion.
I think you're probably
so short-tempered
because you're not
as open minded as I am.
[RIMURU] That aside, I'd like
to be on good terms with humans.
Ideally, I want to open up
a trade network
with you all someday.
Seriously?
[RIMURU]
Fo' sho.
We're already negotiating
with the Dwarven Kingdom.
Wait, with Dwargon?
Being able to pass
through our land
would probably make
things much easier
for traveling merchants.
Don't you think?
Stop, let's back up.
Dwargon acknowledged
this monster town
as a legitimate nation?
If you want, I could confirm
that information.
[FUZE]
Minister Vesta!
Former minister.
But I don't understand this.
What are you doing here?
[ALL]
Huh?
[VESTA] Trying to put
my talents to good use.
Anyway, what Lord Rimuru
has said is the truth.
He and King Gazel
have entered into
an official treaty together.
[FUZE gasps]
[YOUM]
Hmm?
[RIMURU]
Now are you convinced?
[ROMMEL]
Hmm.
[FUZE]
I mean, if that's the case,
then we aren't exactly opposed
to cooperating
with you or anything.
Still though,
we'll need some kind of proof
that you're an ally of humans.
Unfortunately, we can't just
take your word for it.
Is that fair?
[RIMURU]
Sure.
I'd expect nothing less.
We'll figure something out.
And you're welcome to stay.
Whatever helps you understand
that we aren't a threat.
I was wondering, though.
Do you know if the news that
the Orc Lord has been defeated
has already gotten around?
Well, no.
Only our king knows the details,
as well as a select
group of people.
[RIMURU]
I see.
Well, then, Youm,
wanna make a contract with me?
Ha. Why would I want to?
[gasps]
[SHION growls]
I mean, why wouldn't I want to?
[RIMURU] You said that
the Kingdom of Falmuth
paid you to
come out here, right?
All you'd be doing
is switching employers.
To put it in layman's terms,
I basically want you guys
to be the champions
who defeated the Orc Lord.
[ALL]
Huh?
[RIMURU] You can tell everyone
that we helped you out.
Then just start a rumor
that you were the one
who defeated the Orc Lord.
And that's pretty much it.
If everything goes
according to plan,
then we become known as the town
of trustworthy friendly monsters
who assisted the champions
in their time of need.
I think it'll be easier
to build a good relationship
with humans
if they think we're cool
instead of
mean-hearted creatures.
What do you think?
[BENIMARU]
It's a good plan.
[SOUEI]
Yes, I agree.
♪
[RIMURU]
Have you given it any thought?
[YOUM]
Yes, I have...
Sir.
It's really something.
After seeing your town,
and the people in it,
I can tell you're not evil.
And it's not like our hands
are completely clean.
But we've longed to be free men.
The only reason
we accepted this mission
was because we had planned
to fake our deaths.
Afterwards, we would head
to a safer nation.
I've decided.
I think I'll trust you.
From now on,
I'll call you "Master Rimuru."
I'm yours to command.
[RIMURU]
Awesome!
You won't regret it.
And that's how Youm
and his companions
began training under Hakurou
in order to start
their new lives as champions.
That didn't take long.
I hope no one saw you, Tear.
[TEAR] How mean.
I am a part of the
Moderate Harlequin Alliance.
Have a little faith in me.
[CLAYMAN chuckling]
Forgive me, I was concerned.
Sometimes you go overboard.
[TEAR]
Nuh-uh.
You don't have to treat me
like a child all the time.
Very well, I'll try.
Anyway, I've just
heard news from Myulan.
It would appear
that Demon Lord Milim
has taken quite a liking
to the majin there.
[TEAR]
Oh?
This is turning out to be more
interesting than I expected.
What a delightful
turn of events.
[TEAR]
That's good, I guess.
But what's the real scoop?
Is this majin really so amazing
that even Milim
would stick around?
Only to the point where he can
no longer be ignored.
He'll never be a match for me,
after all.
Laplace thinks differently.
[TEAR]
How so?
[CLAYMAN]
He said there's an eeriness,
or something of that nature.
[TEAR]
Fascinating.
If a cunning guy
like Laplace says so,
then there must be
something to it.
At the very least,
I think we should investigate
why Demon Lord Milim
is so interested in this majin.
I agree.
We certainly need to gather
more information
and give it
all some thought.
[TEAR]
Yeah, that would be fun!
But back to what I found out.
Let's hear it.
[TEAR]
As it turns out,
Lady Frey has no interest
in the Great Forest of Jura.
She seems worried
about somethin'.
It kinda looked like she was
preparing for a fight!
And did you find out
what that might be?
[TEAR]
I did, and you won't believe it.
She was freaking out,
saying Charybdis
was gonna be revived.
[CLAYMAN gasps]
"Charybdis"?
♪
Interesting.
You know, Tear,
I think I have another task
for you to handle.
[TEAR laughs]
I was hoping you would.
I've already called up Footman,
and we're definitely
ready for a fight.
Good, I'm glad to hear it.
However, I'd like you to avoid
violence this time around.
To start, go find
the location of the seal
and see whether or not
it's possible to tame Charybdis.
That's your new mission.
[TEAR]
Leave it to me, Clayman.
-[CLAYMAN] The location should--
-[TEAR] I said leave it to me!
Okay. I'll see you later.
Charybdis.
I see.
Rumored to have enough power
to rival a Demon Lord.
Yes, it will be
interesting to see
what this monster is like.
[CLAYMAN laughing]
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Evil Creeps Closer."