[NARRATOR]
Veldora the Storm Dragon
was sealed by
"Unlimited Imprisonment."
In order to break the spell,
Rimuru had to eat Veldora
and store him in his stomach.
They both began
to analyze the seal.
Veldora from the inside
and Rimuru from the outside.
All in hopes of one day
setting the dragon free.
Rimuru wandered the cave
where he gained new skills
and finally found the exit.
That's where he ran
into the goblins.
Before he knew it, he found
himself vowing
to help them in the battle
against the Direwolves.
♪
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
Most of these goblins
don't look like
they could do
much damage to a Direwolf.
They lack that warrior vibe.
And muscles.
I might have bitten off
more than I can chew.
Do you all understand
our situation?
Yes. We are prepared to fight
against the Direwolves
even if it costs us our lives.
[GOBLINS grunt]
[RIMURU]
No need to get worked up.
Just be chill.
What matters is that we go out
there and do the best we can.
That's how
a general talks, right?
[clears throat]
Okay, can someone please
show me your wounded?
We did the best that we could
but it's not enough.
[RIMURU]
This is worse than I imagined.
I had no idea the wolves
could cause such a deep wound.
Well, might as well
try eating him.
Wait.
What are you doing, my lord?
[RIMURU grunts]
[moans]
What the... My wounds.
[gasps]
But how?
You healed me.
[RIMURU] I can't believe
that actually worked.
I was kinda shooting
from the hip
when I slurped him up
and smacked him
with a couple
of those potions I made.
They're even more effective
than I thought they would be.
You get a potion,
and you get a potion.
I ate enough of those
hipokute herbs
that I've got loads to spare.
Everyone gets one!
[grunting]
Wow. You truly are
magnificent, my lord.
[GOBLINS gasp]
[RIMURU] There, that's the last
of the wounded.
Now, then,
about the village,
we'll need to fortify it
with a fence.
[ALL]
Hm!
[low growling]
[DIREWOLF BOSS]
Tonight is the night.
Veldora's protection
has vanished from this forest.
We have nothing left to fear.
Under this moon, we'll destroy
the Goblin Village
and create a foothold
for ourselves here
in the Great Forest of Jura.
[howling]
[DIREWOLF BOSS] The Direwolves
shall rule over this forest.
[howling]
Our mighty claws can tear
through any monster,
and our great fangs can break
through the strongest armor.
[howling]
[growls]
[DIREWOLF BOSS scoffs]
What a disgraceful little fence.
They dare mock us?
[DIREWOLF]
Father, look.
[DIREWOLF BOSS]
A slime?
[RIMURU] Turn back now
and nobody gets hurt.
This is your only warning.
[DIREWOLF BOSS]
You insolent wretch.
Do you think a Direwolf
would really listen
to a foolish slime?
Destroy their pitiful fence.
Water the grass
with the blood of goblins!
[GOBLINS gasp]
♪
-[laughs]
-[goblin grunts]
-Huh?
-[grunts]
[grunts]
[whimpers]
Hmm.
[DIREWOLF BOSS]
What's that?
[RIMURU]
It's my skill, Steel Thread.
[DIREWOLF BOSS]
This is your doing?
[RIMURU]
That's right.
[DIREWOLF BOSS] A puny monster
dares to attack us?
I will squash you like a bug!
[DIREWOLF]
Father!
♪
[growls]
[groans]
[roaring]
Lord Rimuru, no!
[grunting]
[RIMURU]
And that's Sticky Thread.
[DIREWOLF BOSS]
This won't stop me.
[RIMURU]
Skill: Water Blade!
[ALL gasp]
[growling]
[RIMURU]
Listen up, Direwolves.
Your boss has been slain.
I'll give you two choices.
You can submit or you can die.
That was stupid.
What will I do if they decide
to take the suicide mission
route and attack all at once?
I wish they'd just choose
the "Run Away" option.
[sighs]
Oh! Predator!
Huh?
[GREAT SAGE]
Analysis complete.
Acquired ability
to mimic Direwolf.
Direwolf species skills
have been acquired,
including
Supreme Sense of Smell,
Thought Communication,
and Menace.
[RIMURU]
Right.
[all gasp]
[RIMURU chuckles]
Hear me.
I will show you mercy
just this once.
If you refuse to yield to me,
then I'll allow you the chance
to turn tail and run.
[roaring]
[RIMURU] Come on, guys,
just run away already.
[roaring continues]
Why aren't they leaving?
Do they still wanna fight?
[whimpers]
[DIREWOLVES]
We yield.
Our pack will now serve you.
[RIMURU] Huh? But they
could have just beat it.
Uh, what the...
Did we win?
Are we safe?
[RIMURU] Yep, all's good
in the goblin hood.
That could have been
a lot worse,
I'm glad that's done.
Like they say,
make love, not war.
[GOBLINS cheering]
[RIMURU] And before
it really had a chance to start,
the great Direwolf battle
at the Goblin Village was over.
Still though...
[indistinct conversations]
[RIMURU]
Now I have a new problem.
Not only do I need
to find someone
to look after these goblins,
I've gotta find
puppy sitters, too.
[murmuring]
[RIMURU] I guess their numbers
are about the same, so...
Listen up, everyone.
[ALL]
Huh?
[RIMURU]
Okay.
Here's what we're going to do
about the living situation.
I'm gonna have you all pair up.
-[GOBLINS] Pair?
-[DIREWOLVES] Up?
[RIMURU]
You seem confused.
We're not sure what you mean
by the term
"pair up," Lord Rimuru.
[RIMURU]
You'll form groups of two.
A group?
[DIREWOLF]
Of two?
[RIMURU]
All right.
Yesterday's enemy
is today's friend.
From this day forward,
I want you all to work together
and get along. Got it?
[ALL]
Yes.
[RIMURU] So help each other out
and have each other's backs.
Ugh.
Guess that settles that problem.
Anyway, moving on.
Next, we'll need to figure out
food, shelter, and clothing.
We should form teams
to hunt and gather food,
build new houses,
and probably get some people
to work on strengthening
the village's defenses.
Let's start with...
Uh, what's that
dude's name again?
Wait, do they even have names?
Yo, Elder, do you guys
have names or what?
Well, it's very unusual
for monsters to have names.
But even without names
we can still communicate
our thoughts to one another.
[RIMURU]
Oh, that's cool.
Still though, it'd be easier
if you all had names.
So, if it's okay with you guys,
I think I'll just give you some.
[all gasp]
Wait. Really?
But are you certain you wanna
give us all a name?
[RIMURU]
Uh, yeah?
-[cheering]
-[howling]
Sheesh. They're weirdly excited
over something as simple
as getting a new name.
[indistinct conversations]
[ELDER muttering]
[RIMURU]
All right, you'll go first.
Let's see, what to call you?
Your son had a name, right?
The one who died in battle?
Yes, it was Rigur.
[RIMURU]
That's cool sounding.
In that case
I'll dub thee, "Rigurd."
[gasps]
To think you've honored me
with such a wondrous name,
you've made me so happy!
[RIMURU]
Jeez, really?
All I did was add a "D"
onto his son's name.
I'm going to call you "Rigur,"
after your brother.
Whoa, thanks!
Oh, my, I can't believe my son
has been allowed
to inherit my other son's name.
[BOTH]
Thank you so much, Lord Rimuru!
[RIGURD] We're not worthy
of your kindness.
[RIMURU] Man, these guys
are way emotional today.
♪
[RIMURU]
Your name's Gobta.
Yay! Thank you.
I'll treasure it, sir.
-[RIMURU] You'll be Gobchi.
-[chuckles]
Uh, Gobtsu.
Gobte.
And uh, you're Gobzo.
-Ooh.
-Yay!
[RIMURU] These names
aren't super imaginative.
I feel bad that they're
so happy about them.
Please, sir.
I certainly don't
want you to think
we're unappreciative
of the names you've given us.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
And we're aware of how strong
your magical power is
compared to ourselves,
but are you sure
it's wise to try
and give everyone a name
in just one sitting?
[RIMURU]
Uh, yeah, I don't see why not.
Well, as long as
you're certain, then.
[RIMURU]
Who's next?
[chuckles]
You'll be Haruna!
'Kay!
♪
[indistinct conversations]
[RIMURU]
Whew.
That takes care
of all of the goblins.
Next up are the wolves.
He's the son
of the Direwolf boss, right?
He might actually be mad at me
for offing his dad.
Then again,
I'm no expert on body language,
but they don't seem upset.
Hmm.
Wolf.
Fangs.
Wind.
Storm.
I know.
I'll give him my family name.
Tempest.
Tempest Fang?
Storm Fang?
Let's see.
Oh. Ranga!
Yeah, that sounds cool!
From now on, you'll be "Ranga!"
[RANGA]
Ranga.
[RIMURU] I guess the tail wag
means he likes it.
[groans]
Hey!
What's with the egg mode
all of a sudden?
[RANGA]
Lord Rimuru?
[RIMURU]
Everything is getting dark.
[MALE GOBLIN]
Oh, no!
[FEMALE GOBLIN]
Somebody do something!
[GREAT SAGE]
Warning.
Internal Magicule reserves
have fallen below minimum limit.
Now entering sleep mode.
Estimated time until
full recovery is three days.
[RIMURU]
I used up too many magicules?
But how?
I couldn't move or speak.
I had no sense
of any of my surroundings,
but I was still conscious.
[crickets chirping]
Oh. This is our fault,
it must be because
he named so many of us
at one time.
[RIMURU] So apparently,
giving out names
like candy to monsters
can use up your magicules.
I guess that's why Rigurd
was acting so weird.
I wonder if
that's common knowledge.
Jeez, he could have
said something.
[howling]
[RIMURU]
And then, three days later...
[birds chirping]
Behold!
I am recovered!
Oh, Lord Rimuru.
You're finally awake.
[RIMURU]
That I am.
You look like you're feeling
much better, now.
[RIMURU]
Who is this?
Hold on, I'll go fetch
Elder Rigurd for you.
[RIMURU]
Uh, okay.
[RIMURU] Huh. Did this village
always have a cute girl in it?
[RIGURD]
Lord Rimuru.
I'm so happy
that you've finally recovered.
Rigurd, hey!
So who was that girl
just now...
-Who the heck are you?!
-[snickers]
[laughs]
It is I, Rigurd.
But weren't you like super old
three days ago?!
Indeed, before you
gave us all names.
I de-aged you?
When a monster is given a name,
it raises their rank
and makes them evolve
into something more powerful,
like the handsome specimen
you see here.
-[chuckles]
-[RIMURU] Uh, cool.
At least that explains
why you guys were so excited
to be getting a name
in the first place.
No wonder that process
sucked my magicules dry.
[RIGURD screams]
[RANGA]
Master, you're awake!
Allow me to express
my utmost joy
that you've finally recovered.
[RIMURU]
Hold on.
Judging by the star
on your forehead,
you're Ranga, right?
Yes!
[RIMURU screaming]
[GOBLINS cheering]
[howling]
[RIMURU]
There's Rigurd.
[laughing]
-[RIMURU] Rigur.
-[chuckles]
-[laughing]
-And Gobta.
Huh, he really didn't
change that much.
[cheering]
I know Rigurd said
they all evolved,
but they almost seem like
completely different monsters.
[GREAT SAGE] The male goblins
have evolved to Hobgoblins,
and the female goblins
have become Goblinas.
[birds chirping]
[RIMURU]
Hey, Ranga.
You were the only Direwolf
I had a chance to name.
So, why is it that the other
Direwolves evolved, too?
[RANGA]
An excellent question.
It's because all of us
Direwolves act as one entity.
You see, in our pack,
we're all connected.
Therefore, my name has also
become our clan's name.
[RIMURU]
Oh.
I get it, so your whole pack
evolved through a shared name.
[RANGA]
Correct.
We are no longer known
as the Direwolves.
We're now the Tempest Wolves.
[RIMURU]
Tempest Wolves.
That sounds pretty awesome.
[RIMURU grunting]
[screaming]
Oh, no, forgive
my tail wagging, master!
[RIMURU] You have to be careful
with that thing, Ranga!
[RANGA]
Unh. I really am sorry.
[RIMURU]
Whoa, you can change your size?
That's convenient.
The monsters evolving
is cool and all,
but the bigger problem here
is what we're gonna do
about finding enough food,
clothing and shelter
to sustain everybody.
[screaming]
[RANGA]
Master, no-o-o!
-[indistinct conversations]
-[laughter]
[huffs]
Right.
It took five whole minutes
for everyone to settle down
and stop gabbing.
Man, that was my best village
elder impression.
[RIGURD] Lord Rimuru,
what's that on your face?
[spits]
Nothing.
What's on your face?
Anyway, as you can all see
we're a big happy family now.
In order to avoid complications,
I think we should
set a few ground rules.
[ALL]
Rules?
There are three rules.
Please do your best
to follow them.
First, no attacking humans.
Second, no fighting
amongst yourselves.
Third, no belittling
other races.
That's it.
[GOBLINS]
Huh? What?
[confused chatter]
-Sir?
-[RIMURU] Yes?
You have a question?
Is there a reason why we're not
allowed to attack the humans?
How dare you question him?!
[RIMURU]
Calm down, Rigurd, it's fine.
It's simple, really.
It's just because
I like humans, that's all.
Okay, then.
Makes perfect sense.
[RIMURU]
Wait, it does? Really?
Uh, good.
[clears throat]
Another thing is,
humans typically live
in large groups.
And if you mess with them then
they might retaliate against us.
If they were to
come after us in earnest
I doubt we could handle them.
Besides, getting along with them
is beneficial to us, too.
[ALL]
Mm-hmm.
[RIMURU]
Are there any other questions?
Me!
Yes, Gobta.
When you say
"Don't belittle other races,"
what's that mean?
Well, you've all gotten stronger
by evolving, right?
It means you shouldn't let that
go to your head
and use that strength
to push others around.
It's not fair to think
you're better than they are.
Besides, what if they
get stronger one day
and choose to start
pushing you around?
We understand you, sir.
[ALL]
Mm-hmm.
[RIMURU]
Okay, that's it.
Do your best
to follow those rules.
[ALL]
Right.
[RIMURU]
One more thing.
Elder Rigurd,
I'd like for you to be in charge
of everyone in this village.
You're the Goblin Lord.
[RIGURD]
The Lord?
[RIMURU]
Lead your village well.
Yes!
Thank you, my lord.
I accept this
great responsibility.
I promise I won't
let you down, sir.
[RIMURU] Good.
I'm counting on you.
I don't wanna tell him
I only dumped the gig on him
because I don't
feel like doing it.
After that, I assigned jobs
to the rest of the goblins.
I formed a team to keep watch
over the village.
Then I made a squad
to gather food.
Regarding those tasks, I think
everything will be fine.
The real problems are...
the group that builds houses
and the people who make clothes.
You know, two thirds
of the whole
"food, shelter, clothing" thing.
Are you sure that's a house?
[BOTH grunt]
[RIMURU] Honestly, I only know
the basics of being a handyman,
but I worked
in general contracting
so I know good from bad.
And this...
would probably get a shutdown
by the health department.
This is most embarrassing.
Forgive us.
[RIMURU] Regarding
the clothing problem...
[chuckles]
[RIMURU] I just think we need
more coverage, is all.
[chuckles]
[RIMURU] Not that
I'm complaining, necessarily.
[RIGUR] We don't have anyone
who's skilled at making clothes.
[RIMURU] Huh? Well, if you
can't make them,
then couldn't you go
buy them somewhere?
Hmm. Yes, now that
I think about it,
there are others we trade
with from time to time.
Not only do they have people
who can make us clothing,
but they might also
have somebody
who knows about
building houses, as well.
[RIMURU] Huh. Well, we aren't
getting anywhere this way.
So maybe we should go see them.
Who are these people?
I'm referring to the Dwarves
that live in Dwargon.
[RIMURU]
Dwarves?!
Like the famous masters
of metalworking Dwarves?
That sounds like
that would be so much fun!
Then I'll travel to Dwargon
on our behalf.
Rigurd, are you cool
with looking after the village
while I'm away?
Yes.
Rest assured that everything
is safe with me and my muscles.
♪
[RIMURU]
All right. You kids behave.
[ALL]
We'll see you later!
-Travel safely.
-[ALL] Bye!
Come back soon, okay?
♪
[RIMURU] And so I left
the village on a new adventure
to go and meet the Dwarves.
The goblins told me
that this Dwargon place is huge,
and it even has its own king.
You gotta admit
that sounds pretty cool!
Onward.
To a new adventure
filled with excitement!
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"In the Kingdom of the Dwarves."