[GOBLINS gasping]
[RIMURU]
Hmm...
[GOBLINS gasp]
[ALL gasp]
Do you like it?
Or is it not to your tastes?
It's good! [laughs]
[cheering]
-Hmm.
-[RIGURD] Hmm. [laughs]
[RIMURU sighs]
This is awesome!
My usual slime form
doesn't have any taste buds.
So this is the first time
I've tasted anything
since I came to this world.
[chuckles]
Man, it's great to be alive!
[GOBLINS cheering]
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
♪
[coughs]
Wait, you mean to tell me
that orcs attacked ogres?
That's crazy.
But it's the truth.
I can't believe it. Can you?
It is surprising.
Wait, so does that mean
it's a big deal?
-Hey, Gobta.
-Of course it is.
Compared to orcs, ogres are
a much stronger people.
That such a weak race would go
and attack them is unthinkable.
Regardless, they did attack.
The orc army struck our village
in the dead of night.
They had weapons...
-and wore armor.
-[roaring]
[YOUNG MASTER]
Their numbers filled the forest
and overwhelmed us.
Those detestable pigs,
destroyed our homes
and my people.
Orcs wearing armor?
That's right.
Similar to what humans wear.
It was full plate mail.
Hmm.
That can only mean...
That the orcs
aren't working alone.
Someone's helping them.
It would make sense,
as they wouldn't be able
to get valuable armor
by themselves.
You would be correct.
Someone was with them.
[inaudible]
[KAIJIN]
A masked majin?
[grunts]
It was extremely powerful.
I'm certain.
[RIGURD] When you saw
Lord Rimuru in the forest,
you believed it was him,
and that's why you attacked?
Yes.
Okay, so what's
all that supposed to mean?
It's only a guess,
but it could mean
that the orcs have sided
with a Demon Lord.
It's hard to know for sure.
Uh yeah, I knew that.
Hmm.
A Demon Lord?
Perhaps, but why side with orcs?
I don't know.
But I can tell you this much,
of my 300 brethren,
only six of us managed
to escape them with our lives.
I see. No wonder
you were so upset.
Are you finished feasting,
Lord Rimuru?
I'm just taking a break.
Man, your sister's
something else.
[YOUNG MASTER gasps]
Hmm.
[RIMURU] She knows so much about
medicinal and cooking herbs
that the goblinas took
to her immediately.
[YOUNG MASTER]
She was a very sheltered child.
I'm sure it makes her happy
to be relied upon.
So, what are you guys
gonna do now?
Wait, what?
As in, what's your next move?
Are you gonna
rebuild your village?
Or maybe relocate
somewhere else?
Your comrades are depending
on your leadership, aren't they?
[grunting]
That's easy. Once we regroup,
we'll go back for revenge.
-Do you know where they are?
-[YOUNG MASTER gasps]
[YOUNG MASTER sighs]
[RIMURU]
AKA, he has no idea.
Mind if I make a suggestion?
How about you guys join me
and become my subordinates?
Join you?
Yeah. I can't give you much.
But I do have food, shelter,
and clothing.
You need a home base, right?
We do, but that might get
your village involved
in our path for revenge.
Well, I'm not just offering this
as a favor to you guys.
You said that there were
thousands of armed orcs
who attacked your village.
And that there might be
a Demon Lord
pulling the strings.
There's also the possibility
that it's part
of a devilish plot
to take over
the Great Forest of Jura.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
Which would mean, our little
village is also in danger.
You guys are strong.
Adding numbers to our ranks
will only benefit us in the end.
And then, if you got into
a fight or something,
I'd help you all out.
I'll never abandon a friend.
I see.
Please let me
give it some thought.
Sure.
Take all the time you need.
On that note,
it's time for round two of
the all-you-can-eat meat.
[indistinct conversations]
[OGRE]
It's not a bad offer.
Still though,
it's your choice to make.
We'll do whatever
you and the princess choose.
[grunts]
[YOUNG MASTER]
If only I were stronger.
[birds chirping]
[RIMURU]
Have you decided?
Yes, the ogres
are a warring clan.
As such, we aren't opposed
to fighting under others.
If our master is strong,
we're more than pleased
to serve them.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
Although, we'll only serve you
until we defeat the orcs.
[RIMURU] Once we win,
you can do whatever you want.
Whether that's staying
to help us build a nation,
or going on your own way.
[exhales]
[inhales]
[YOUNG MASTER] In that case,
I accept your offer.
Myself and the other ogres
shall serve under you.
[RIMURU]
Good.
I didn't really think
about what he must be feeling.
I'm sure all he wants
is to avenge his people,
even if it means his own death.
This is a choice he's made,
not just as a leader,
but also as someone who's had
to accept his own weakness.
Lift your head.
Thank you for accepting.
-Call in the others.
-Right.
[RIMURU]
All I can do is make sure
he doesn't come to
regret that choice.
♪
Mm-hmm.
I'll give you names to mark you
as my subordinates.
[ALL gasp]
To all of us, my lord?
Why wouldn't I?
It makes things easier.
Are you sure?
Please, don't do this.
Naming someone uses a lot
of power and is very risky.
And we're already strong.
It'll be fine, you don't have
to worry about me.
But...
[RIMURU] The only risk is me
using too many magicules
and falling asleep.
Besides, there's only
six of them,
how bad could it be?
Are you trying to tell me
that you'd rather pass
on the name thing?
Well, not exactly.
We accept.
[PRINCESS]
Big Brother.
It would be our honor.
[OLD MAN] We will do whatever
the young master wishes.
Hmm.
All right, then.
Your name is...
-[RIMURU groaning]
-[thuds]
[PRINCESS] Shion. Come on,
it's time to switch places.
[SHION]
Don't worry, princess.
I'm more than happy
to look after Lord Rimuru.
Why don't you go get some rest?
[PRINCESS]
I'm not even tired.
-[RIMURU] Huh?
-[SHION gasps]
[BOTH] Lord Rimuru.
You're finally awake.
[RIMURU]
Uh, who are you again?
Man. I'm trying to remember,
but my memory's all fuzzy.
I was getting ready
to name the ogres when...
Wait.
[YOUNG MASTER] It's good to have
you back among us, Lord Rimuru.
[RIMURU] Are you
the young master of the ogres?
Correct. Though now I have
evolved into a Kijin.
Thanks to my new name.
Benimaru.
[RIMURU]
Oh. Now I remember.
I went into sleep mode
the moment I named them.
Hold on. "Kijin"?
What happened to the ogre part?
[GREAT SAGE] "Kijin" refers
to a race of beings
uncommonly born of ogres.
[RIMURU]
Cool.
His body looks
smaller and more human.
But even though
he looks less imposing,
the amount of magicules
he possesses has exploded.
Whoa, this is like
the Rigurd incident
all over again.
I had no idea that an ogre
could evolve into a Kijin.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Shuna.
I'm so happy
that you're finally awake.
[RIMURU]
Shuna.
Right, the ogre princess.
She was already cute, but now
she's just plain beautiful.
I'm Shion. I adore the name
you've bestowed upon me.
Thank you so much, my lord.
[RIMURU]
This busty babe is Shion?
She looks a little less wild
and a little more refined.
And behind
the young leader, Benimaru,
is the old guy who managed
to cut off my arm.
[laughs]
Is that how you remember me?
I must admit I was surprised
when you instantly grew
a new one.
[RIMURU] He seems to be
a lot younger now.
Is that a result
of his evolution to a Kijin?
Uh...
And your name was?
You have given me
the name of "Souei."
I'm grateful, and happy
that you've recovered, my lord.
[RIMURU]
Uh, thanks.
[GREAT SAGE] Giving a name
to a superior monster
consumes an equally
large amount of magicules.
[RIMURU] In other words,
naming just the six of them
completely drained
my magicule bank?
These are the kinds of things
I need to know sooner.
[gasps]
Where's the other guy?
Oh. He's been spending
quite a bit of time
at Kaijin's workshop.
[MAN] Is it true
that Lord Rimuru woke up?
Ah. Here he comes now.
[RIMURU]
He used to look like this.
I wonder how he's changed.
-[MAN] Lord Rimuru.
-[RIMURU] Huh?
I'm so glad
that you've recovered.
[RIMURU gasps]
It's me, sir.
I'm Kurobe, remember?
[RIMURU]
He looks like a normal dude!
There's a hot guy, a cute girl,
a babe, the dignified elder,
hot guy number two.
I'm actually glad the last one
is so boringly normal.
Well, I hope
we'll be good friends.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
[rumbling]
♪
[RIMURU]
Meanwhile, the changes occurring
in the Great Forest of Jura
continued their
invasive progress.
There's a place out
in the middle
of the Great Forest of Jura
called Lake Siss.
The lake is surrounded
by vast marshlands.
The Lizardmen control
this territory.
[LIZARDMAN]
Sir. Reporting.
There's an Orc Army.
Just south of Lake Siss.
We think they may be coming
to invade our territory.
An orc army?
We must prepare for battle.
We'll beat those
disgusting pigs easily.
How many orcs are there?
About that,
when we counted the orcs,
there were a lot.
Two hundred thousand or so.
That's impossible.
Their army is
20 times our size?
We verified the number
using Magic Sense
and Sense Heat Source.
I swear on my life
that this information is true.
I trust you.
You are excused for now.
[BOTH]
Sir.
[CHIEFTAIN]
Two hundred thousand?
How do they feed such
a ridiculously large army?
Orcs are rather ravenous
creatures to start with.
And they're supposed
to be uncoordinated,
so how did they form
an entire army?
Even if someone
assembled the beasts,
actually controlling them would
be another matter altogether.
Know what I heard?
There's a rumor
that they recently destroyed
an ogre village.
[BOTH]
Say what now?
[CHIEFTAIN]
An Orc Lord.
[ALL gasp]
If there was anyone
capable of commanding an army
of two hundred thousand Orcs,
as he said,
it would have to be
the Unique monster.
I've only heard legends,
but it's known as an Orc Lord.
-Wait, a real Orc Lord?
-That's impossible!
No, if anything
it makes perfect sense.
That's the only way
anyone could command
such a formidable army of orcs
without losing control of them.
But what could the Orc Lord
possibly want?
As if any of that
actually matters.
The real question
is can we defeat their army?
[CHIEFTAIN]
If what we are facing
is in fact a true Orc Lord,
it will be difficult
for us to win.
[ALL gasp]
[CHIEFTAIN] Because the Orc Lord
is a true monster,
capable of devouring the fear
and anxiety of its own allies.
However, we can't
be sure just yet.
Still, we must prepare
to the best of our abilities.
And what do you mean by that?
We'll need to try
and arrange some back up.
Where's my son?
Has anyone seen him lately?
[SON]
I'm right here, Father.
Though, I must say
it's a bit hurtful
that you address me
in such a boorish manner.
You may recall
that I have a name.
It's Gabiru, and it was given
to me by Lord Gelmud himself.
What I call my son
should make no difference.
[CHIEFTAIN'S DAUGHTER scoffs]
[GABIRU grunts]
In any case, I have
an important task for you.
And what would that be?
[shouting]
Too slow. Move faster.
[GOBLINS grunting]
-Sheesh.
-[ALL groaning]
Come on. Aren't you
going to strike me back?
[grunting]
[RIMURU]
Gobta made the mistake of saying
he wanted to learn
swordsmanship, so here we are.
Hakurou is definitely
a tough teacher.
[RANGA panting]
[RIMURU]
Orc Lord? What's that?
Well, to put it rather simply,
it's a monster.
[RIMURU]
Thanks for that in-depth answer.
They're incredibly rare beasts.
Born to the orcs
only every few centuries.
It is a Unique monster.
[RIMURU]
Unique, huh?
[BENIMARU]
It's said they're capable
of devouring their comrades'
fear and anxiety,
which would make them
an unnaturally effective leader.
[RIMURU]
Yikes.
When they attacked our village,
they seemed unfazed by
the deaths of their own people.
Hence my suspicion.
[RIMURU]
I see.
[panting]
[BENIMARU] Of course,
all things considered,
it's only a possibility.
[GOBLINS screaming]
[RIMURU]
It's so weird though.
Why would they wanna attack
your village in the first place?
Good question.
I'm not sure
if there's a connection.
But shortly before the attack,
a majin visited our village.
[GELMUD]
I shall give you a name.
That's what he told me,
but he seemed untrustworthy.
Naturally I refused,
and he cursed me
as he left our village.
[RIMURU]
A majin, huh?
So you think that dude
is mad at you
for refusing his name gift?
I didn't have a choice.
I'd never want a gift
from such an unsuitable master.
I am rather particular.
So I wouldn't accept a name
from just anyone.
[RIMURU gasping]
[BENIMARU]
What was the majin's name?
Let's see. Geli. Gele.
Maybe Gela? Or Gelo?
[BOTH gasp]
It's Gelmud.
Right. That's it.
[RIMURU]
Gelmud?
Weird, for some reason
that name is ringing a bell.
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
Hey, Rigur.
I was wondering, who was it
that named your brother?
Sir. I'm told
that he received his name
from a passing demon
called Lord Gelmud.
-He saw promise in him.
-[RIMURU] Gel what?
Oh, Lord Gelmud.
He's from the Demon Lord's army.
[RIMURU]
I bet it's the same guy.
Man, he passes out names
like candy. But why?
Is this a good time?
-I have news.
-[RIMURU] Sure.
I saw a group of Lizardmen
not far from here.
[RIMURU]
Lizardmen? Not orcs?
Correct. Typically, they make
their home in the marshlands.
It seemed unnatural
for them to stray so far away.
And so, I thought
you should know.
[RIMURU sighs]
[SOUEI] It appears they were
attempting negotiations
with a nearby goblin village.
Which means, it's likely
they'll come here next.
[RIMURU]
I see. Lizardmen, huh?
[wind blowing]
[GOBLINS groaning]
[birds chirping]
Honestly, my father
can be so paranoid.
Go visit the nearby
goblin villages
and enlist their aid.
[GABIRU]
Whatever!
Since when did we,
the esteemed Lizardman race,
begin to fear a bunch of fat,
disgusting orcs?
You know, once upon a time,
Father used to be
such a proud and noble leader.
That's true, maybe you should
be the chieftain, Sir Gabiru.
[GABIRU gasps]
[GABIRU]
Oh, no, if anything,
my comment
was a bit disrespectful.
I still fall quite a bit short
when it comes to my father.
You think so?
But as you are now,
I bet you're just as mighty
as the chieftain
-during his glory days.
-True.
No. I mean, not really.
Sir. You have a name.
He doesn't.
Yes, and no one
can match your skill
when it comes to the spear.
If you don't take your
stand now, then when will you?
[gasps]
[GABIRU]
Uh... Uh...
Wait, does that mean...
Is it possible that
I'm actually...
pretty incredible?!
Well, then.
Perhaps you're right.
My father's grown old.
And it may take a bit of force,
but I'm determined to show him
that I have the strength worthy
of a true Lizardman chieftain.
[ALL]
That's the spirit, sir!
[GABIRU]
Then he can retire
knowing that our clan
is in capable hands.
So?
[chuckles softly]
Yes.
♪
Once I drive away
this pesky orc army,
I shall take my rightful place
as the next Lizardman chieftain.
Yay, that's our
Sir Gabiru. Whoo!
-You're the best!
-Glad I thought of it.
-[cheering continues]
-[GABIRU chuckles] Hmm.
-[ALL] Gabiru! Gabiru!
-Let's go!
-[ALL] Gabiru!
-[GABIRU grunts]
All right then, comrades,
follow me, to a brighter future!
[ALL cheering]
[LIZARDMEN]
Gabiru! Gabiru! Gabiru!
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time, "Gabiru is Here."