[RIMURU]
The Calamity level monster,
Charybdis, has awakened
and is heading straight towards
the capital city of Rimuru.
I think it's after me.
Maybe. Probably.
♪
We've assembled
multiple forces
to fight Charybdis.
They consist
of Benimaru's group,
the Goblin Riders,
the High Orcs led by Geld,
Gabiru and his crew,
and some help
that's just arrived
from King Gazel.
One hundred Pegasus Knights,
led by
the captain of the guard, Dorf.
This way we have
an air-based combat force.
[GAZEL scoffs]
It's only natural
that I send aid to Rimuru
considering I am his mentor.
Sir.
[RIMURU] For some reason
King Gazel has labeled me
as his apprentice or whatever.
Well, let's do this.
[ALL]
Right.
♪
Hell Flare, go!
[RIMURU]
That's Benimaru for you,
nuking things like
nobody's business, but...
It's shocking
that my brother's attack
wasn't strong enough
to destroy it.
[RIMURU] There's gotta be
a reason, right?
[GREAT SAGE] Notice.
Charybdis has the Extra Skill
Magic Jamming.
It reduces the efficiency
of any magic used
within a 300-meter radius
of the creature.
[RIMURU] Things just got
a whole lot harder.
Okay, first let's scatter
and take out the megalodons.
[grunting]
[yelling]
[grunts]
I'll keep it from moving,
you guys just focus
on taking it out!
[ORC]
On it!
[grunting]
[yelling]
Attack!
[ALL yelling]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[GELD]
Great, now what?
With my men down for the count,
how am I supposed
to beat this thing?
[GABIRU]
Allow me to lend you a hand!
[GELD gasps]
Vortex Crash!
You're the best, Sir Gabiru.
-It's true.
-Treat the injured.
Sir, yes, sir!
[GABIRU] Just so you know, I was
only able to get a clear shot
because you were holding
the megalodon in place.
I appreciate the assist, Gabiru.
[GABIRU gasps]
We'll bring that one down,
then leave the rest to you guys.
[GELD]
Right.
Don't worry, we can handle it.
[grunts]
Yeah, go get 'em, Sir Gabiru.
Come on, men, let's show
these wretched beasts
what the Pegasus Knights
are capable of!
[ALL yelling]
[ALL shouting]
[ALL screaming]
Oh! Oh, no, run away!
[ALL yelling]
[GOBTA screaming]
[laughs]
They served as
an excellent diversion.
In battle, some will attack
and some will play
a different role.
All parts are important.
Hakurou's no joke.
He does not mess around.
Regaining his youth
has allowed him
to refine
his tough teaching style.
Hey! I wanna play with
the shark monsters, too.
What are you doing here?
I thought I told you
to wait back in town.
Yeah, but you never said
I couldn't watch.
Staying in town was so boring!
Just let me kill
one of ‘em, okay?
-No way!
-[MILIM] Huh?
[MILIM whimpering]
Those sad eyes
won't work on me.
Master Souei, do it now.
[SOUEI]
Right.
How do you like
my Puppet Strings?
[roaring]
[BOTH gasp]
♪
[growling]
[MILIM]
Ooh!
He's using his strings to make
the megalodons fight each other!
He's got good looks
and good skills.
It's so unfair.
Finish off the one
we just took down.
As you command, sir.
Leave the rest to us.
♪
Hold up. When exactly
did Ranga learn how to fly?
And when did he and Shion
decide to team up?
I'll prove to Lord Rimuru
how valuable I can be
in a battle.
[RANGA] Indeed. We shall prove
our worth together!
[SHION yelling]
Decapitating Demon Blade!
[howling]
I just wanna
destroy them a little.
Sorry, but the answer's
still no.
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[chuckles softly]
All finished. Next up.
♪
[RANGA]
I'm ready when you are.
Let's see how strong
that thing is.
Sounds like a good plan.
-[ALL screaming]
-[MEGALODON growling]
♪
[GOBTA groaning]
[HAKUROU]
I'm disappointed.
You couldn't even stop
one megalodon.
I'll admit that you've improved
a bit since we started,
but in the future, I think
you'll benefit
from tougher training.
Huh? No way, old man, if it gets
any tougher, we'll all die!
Old man, you say?
[chuckling nervously]
[GOBTA screaming]
Lord Rimuru.
I think Charybdis
is all that's left.
Fortunately, we have
a formidable army.
Look there.
♪
Yeah, but that thing's
so big, though.
[GREAT SAGE] Answer.
Judging from its size, the--
[RIMURU] If you're gonna
tell me anything,
then it needs to be
how to defeat that monster.
And nothing.
♪
Doesn't look like they're
doing much damage to it.
I agree.
[RIMURU] It might be
gearing up for something.
-Don't let your guard down!
-Understood.
-[SOUEI] Right.
-[RANGA] Thank you, master.
We'll be careful.
-[CHARYBDIS growling]
-[SHION gasps]
Watch out! Get away!
[ALL scream]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[SOUEI]
I can't dodge.
Dodge? Don't be a coward!
[groans]
[howling]
[SHION and SOUEI panting]
[RANGA]
Souei, use Shadow Movement
and get out of here.
I will stay and shield Shion.
No, Ranga. Don't be an idiot.
I'll fight by myself.
[RANGA laughs]
I can't leave, not when
our master would want you
to have
the highest chance of survival.
You're right,
he would want that.
I think I'll stay, too.
Besides, if anything goes wrong,
the real me can withdraw
before I get killed.
-So there's that.
-[SHION chuckles]
Typical Souei.
Well, okay, then I guess
we'd better all survive.
Hyah!
[grunts]
[ALL yelling]
[RIMURU] You idiots
need to simmer down.
After all, I've got
some pretty legit skills, too.
[SHION]
Lord Rimuru.
[RIMURU]
Devour all! Gluttony!
[SHION gasps]
[SOUEI] He dissolved
all those scales instantly.
Leave this dude to me.
I want you guys to fall back
for now and get some rest.
But we can still help you.
Just take it easy.
And besides...
the scales
are already regenerating.
If it uses
that same move again,
I might not be able
to protect you in time.
Let me take over
for a while.
You guys wait
for Benimaru's orders.
As you command.
Please be careful, Lord Rimuru.
[RANGA]
Once I've rested,
I shall return
to help you, master.
Sounds good.
[grunts]
Now, then, let's see
if I can do some damage!
[yells]
♪
[groaning]
Oh, wow.
[grunts]
It looks
a little damaged.
Maybe.
Still...
does Charybdis have
rapid regeneration or something?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
Judging from the speed at which
it repairs its body tissue,
it is safe to assume
that the individual, Charybdis,
possesses the Extra Skill
Ultraspeed Regeneration.
Aw, no!
[GREAT SAGE] It is estimated
that because of this skill
it will regenerate its scales
within three minutes.
So there's only three minutes
until it can launch
that attack again.
[exhales]
[groans]
Okay. Utilize all methods
at your disposal and attack.
No matter what, we can't give it
the opportunity to recover!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[RIMURU] The support
of the Pegasus Knights
increased our strength
more than tenfold.
So I really thought we'd be
able to take Charybdis down
with an all-out attack.
[RIMURU sighs]
We've been at this for hours,
but we barely damaged the thing.
Our strongest attacks
only knocked its health down
by 30 percent.
What should we do?
[CHARYBDIS groaning]
-[RIMURU] Huh?
-[CHARYBDIS] Damn you.
Mi... Mi... Milim!
[groaning]
Wait, "Milim"?
Did I hear that right?
Hey, Great Sage, use Appraisal.
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
Signs of life identified in
the body occupied by Charybdis.
The body appears to possess
an intense anger.
So the dude's angry? At Milim?
So basically, Giant Eye-ball
Fish Guy was heading to town
because he has a bone to pick
with our
honey-loving Demon Lord?
Meaning he doesn't give a crap
about me or Veldora at all.
Talk about overthinking it.
Hold up.
I've made Milim sit
on the sidelines for nothing.
And she's asleep!
-Milim!
-[gasps]
[shudders]
I've definitely been awake
the whole time, I swear!
No, you were definitely asleep.
I was just meditating.
And silently cheering you on
with my eyes closed!
[sighs]
I'm sure.
Anyway, the giant tuna thing
apparently has business
with you.
Really?!
Oh, yeah, it looks like
it possessed that Phobio guy
who ticked me off the other day.
[inaudible]
The Beastketeer?
Okay.
Well, I had you sit out
because I thought
he was after me,
but I guess he's not, so...
Are you trying to say
that I'm allowed
to pulverize him now?!
[chuckles]
[MILIM laughs]
I feel kinda bad
about all this.
Looks like you could have been
helping the whole time.
As long as I get to play
with him now, it's okay.
-I'll crush him.
-Oh, hold on.
Didn't Phobio say
something about working
for Demon Lord Carrion?
Is there anyway you can
kill it, but save him?
[laughing]
Easy work for someone like me.
I actually possess
a lot of restraint, you know.
Uh...
[RIMURU]
She does? Since when?
[DORF] All units,
fall back immediately!
[CHARYBDIS grunts]
[growls]
Milim! Milim!
Yeah, yeah,
I've already seen that trick.
But you haven't seen
any of my moves yet.
Now, I'll show you
what restraint looks like!
[energy charging]
Drago Buster!
[explosions]
[RIMURU] Maybe we define
"restraint" differently.
There he is. [grunts]
Gotcha.
Now that's what
I call restraint.
[MILIM chuckles]
[heart thumping]
[GREAT SAGE]
Notice.
The magicore of Charybdis
has been completely removed
from Phobio's body
and consumed.
Preparing to isolate it
and begin Appraisal.
[sighs]
-[RIMURU] Hmm?
-[BENIMARU] Hmm.
[water splashes]
[energy humming]
That should fix him up.
[DORF]
Lord Rimuru.
[RIMURU] Hey, Dorf.
Thanks again for all your help.
We couldn't have taken down
Charybdis without you.
No. We didn't do anything
to Charybdis at all.
Huh?
[DORF] Can you explain
what's going on here?
Well, sort of.
Would you believe me
if I told you
this was Demon Lord Milim? Hah.
[DORF]
Hmm?
Hmm.
Truly?
[MILIM]
Mm-hmm!
[laughs]
I see you have a fondness
for pranks, Lord Rimuru.
-[MILIM gasps]
-In the future,
should you possess a similar
powerful magical weapon,
do try and use it at the start
of the battle instead.
It's not a prank,
I'm a real live Demon Lord,
damn it!
I blew Charybdis to pieces!
I see.
You want to keep
your weapon a secret.
Well, I understand.
Keeping your trump card
to yourself
is a wise move, you know.
I'm telling you, I killed it!
[DORF] Charybdis could have
rained all sorts of disasters
down on the world,
so its defeat benefits us all.
I suppose we should
take our leave
and get back to the king,
I'm sure he'll be
awaiting my report.
-[MILIM] Don't ignore me!
-Thank you again for your help.
And please give King Gazel
my regards.
[RIMURU]
Hey. You awake?
[groaning]
What the... Where am I?
And what the heck happened?
[RIMURU] Are you saying
you don't remember what you did?
[PHOBIO gasps]
Please forgive me!
I've done something
unthinkable to Lady Milim!
And worse, I've involved
all of you in it as well.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, but why?
How did you know where Charybdis
was sealed in the forest?
It would be nearly impossible
for you to just stumble upon it.
-[RIMURU] Answer them.
-[PHOBIO] Of course.
You see...
Hold on.
Masked Harlequins
named Footman and Tear?
Did the mask look like this?
[PHOBIO]
No, the ones I met
were a girl with a tear
under one eye,
and a heavy-set man
whose mask had an angry face.
[gasps]
Wait. I wonder
if it was Laplace?
-[RIMURU] Who?
-He's a clown, too.
Laplace said he was
a servant of Lord Gelmud
when we spoke before battling
with the Orc Lord.
He was wearing a mask like
the one Treyni drew in the dirt.
[RIMURU gasps]
[GABIRU] Also, I think he said
he was the vice president
of some
jack-of-all-trades group,
called the
Moderate Harlequin Alliance.
[RIMURU] So, the dots
are all connected.
I see.
And you say this man
goes by the name of Laplace?
Footman, huh?
I'll take great care
not to forget that name.
Yes. Me, too.
[RIMURU]
So there's a mysterious group
called the
Moderate Harlequin Alliance.
And they pretend to help you,
but in reality they're
fulfilling their own goals
without getting
their hands dirty.
Sounds like a big bag of nope.
[MILIM]
Hmm?
Hey, why are you looking at me?
I don't know them, though,
if these clown people
really do exist,
I think they'd be fun
to meet one day.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
And also,
maybe it wasn't Gelmud.
It could be that Clayman's
actually plotting something
in secret.
So there.
[RIMURU]
Why him?
[MILIM gasps]
[MILIM] Well, he's really
scheme-y like that.
[RIMURU]
Demon Lord Clayman, huh?
[PHOBIO] Regardless of
whoever's scheme it was,
what happened
is my own responsibility.
It's not
Demon Lord Carrion's fault.
So please, take my life,
but leave him out of this.
[RIMURU] Meh, next time
don't let a couple of clowns
make a fool out of you.
[PHOBIO gasps]
[RIMURU]
I think we're good here.
See you around.
But I...
What I did was unforgivable.
[RIMURU] Bro, if I say
we're cool, then we're cool.
Right, Milim?
Right you are, Rimuru.
I did think about giving Phobio
just one good punch,
but I'm far too mature
for such actions.
[RIMURU] You admit you thought
about it, though.
I'm not still mad at you,
so don't even worry about it.
[RIMURU] There you have it.
We're all good.
For sure.
-Is that okay with you, Carrion?
-[ALL gasp]
[gasps]
[PHOBIO]
Lord Carrion!
[scoffs]
So, you knew I was here, Milim?
[MILIM]
Yeah, naturally.
[RIMURU]
This guy is Demon Lord Carrion?
Hey, thanks for being
so understanding
and sparing my foolish
servant's life.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
[CARRION]
So you're the masked majin
that defeated Gelmud?
[RIMURU]
Yep, that's me.
Are you here to avenge him?
[scoffs]
I'll pass. Get up.
[PHOBIO]
Yes, sir.
[gasps]
[loud thud]
-Sorry about that.
-[RIMURU] Huh?
My subordinate got carried away.
And it's my fault for not
keeping a closer eye on him.
Please forgive him.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Thank you. I'll owe you one.
If anything comes up
in the future,
you can count on me.
[RIMURU]
Now that you mention it,
what do you think about
possibly entering
into a non-aggression pact
with our nation?
[CARRION]
Is that all you want?
Fine then.
We can sort this out right now.
On behalf of Eurazania,
in the name of
the Beast Master, Carrion,
I swear that I'll never raise
a blade against your nation.
Thanks.
Sure.
Come on, let's go.
That dude's bleeding everywhere!
We're bound to meet
again soon, Rimuru.
Okay, then.
It's all over.
Let's go home, guys.
[ALL]
Right!
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Yuuki Kagurazaka."