[laughing]
I still can't believe
that happened earlier.
After I busted my ass,
you made 19 flawless long-swords
like it was nothing.
[RIMURU]
They were only flawless
because they were copies
of your original.
I just analyzed
your incredible work
and then used that
magisteel cluster to copy it.
Huh?
[RIMURU]
Sorry if that was out of line.
[MEN sigh]
[sighs]
Honestly, it is
a little frustrating.
No matter, I suppose next time
I'll just have to make a weapon
so amazing that even you
won't be able to copy it,
I'd relish a challenge.
[RIMURU]
That's the spirit!
And speaking of spirits,
refill please.
Can you even taste this,
Mister Slime?
No, I can't.
But, hey, any drink is delicious
if it's being poured
by a pretty lady
such as yourself.
My, what a smooth talker.
Here. Enjoy.
[RIMURU] It's nice being on
this side of the entertaining.
In my old life, it was always me
pouring the drinks
and being overly attentive.
Ahh, this new life rules!
Meanwhile,
Gobta had nothing to do
but hang out
back at the guard house.
[snoring]
[chuckling]
I'd love another.
Oh, hey. Mister Slime.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Would you like to try
something special?
[gasps]
[WOMAN]
This is a talent of mine.
In fact, everyone in town says
I'm the best at it.
Whoa! Shut up!
Is this what I think
it's going to be?
[WOMAN moaning]
[RIMURU]
When she says "special..."
[WOMAN moans]
Oh, my!
[RIMURU]
Is it that kind of special?!
Uh, really?
Like right here?
[gasps]
But, ma'am, people will see!
[WOMAN]
Mister Slime?
[RIMURU]
We can't, we mustn't!
-[WOMAN] Mister Slime.
-[RIMURU gasps]
So, are you ready?
[RIMURU yells]
Aw, man.
Fortune-telling.
What kind of things
can you see with that?
Hmm.
Let's see.
Anything, really.
[sighs]
How about who he's
destined to be with?
-Huh?
-[ALL] Huh?
Hmm?
Yeah. Great idea.
Okay, here I go.
Ta-da!
Oh, no. I don't see anything.
-Aw.
-Hey!
[laughing]
I'm only teasing you.
I can't believe you fell for it.
[RIMURU]
Ugh. Meanie.
'Kay. I'm doing it
for real this time.
-[ALL] Huh?
-[MAN] Hmm?
Hmm?
[RIMURU sighs]
[RIMURU] The person
I'm supposed to be with.
Is it possible I have
a soul mate here?
Could there be a Missus Slime
waiting for me somewhere?
[FORTUNE-TELLER]
There, I see something.
[RIMURU gasps]
♪
[inaudible]
[RIMURU]
She kinda looked Japanese.
[KAIJIN]
Now that was a pretty lady.
[RIMURU gasps]
You're turning red.
Gah! I don't change colors.
Oh. I see.
Are you curious
about the girl you saw?
No fair.
What about me?
[RIMURU]
Of course I'm curious.
I wonder what she's like.
If she's the one
I'm destined to be with
then I'd like to meet her.
[VESTA]
My, this is interesting.
Should you really be wasting
your time drinking?
Hmm.
Good evening, Kaijin.
Great, it's Minister Vesta.
[RIMURU]
Ah, so that's the guy.
He looks like somebody
wound his strings too tight.
Honestly, I'm surprised
you're playing around like this.
Especially since the deadline
for those swords
is fast approaching.
I turned them in earlier.
You know what will happen
if you don't finish them.
Wait. You're already done?
That's right.
With all 20 of them.
But that can't be.
It's true, you wanna
see the invoice?
[clears throat]
No, that's all right.
Besides, finishing one's work...
[RIMURU] It feels like
this minister dude
might have given Kaijin
what he thought
was an impossible order.
...doing your job...
[RIMURU] They don't seem
like they get along.
Honestly, I'm more concerned
with that creature.
[RIMURU]
Who? Me?
This is a nice place.
I can't believe
you would have the audacity
to bring
that disgusting thing inside
and serve it like a guest.
Just looking at it
makes me queasy.
So, since when do you
allow monsters
inside your establishment?
While it is a monster,
it's only a harmless
little slime.
Yet, you do acknowledge
it is a monster.
Or are you inferring
that because it's little,
it doesn't count?
No, it's not that.
Really.
Here you are, Minister.
Have a drink, it's on the house.
Please. Enjoy.
[scoffs]
Very well.
I'll show you
what this monster deserves.
-[ALL gasp]
-[WOMAN] Mister Slime!
[RIMURU]
Don't worry about me, I'm fine.
Did anything get on your dress?
[WOMAN]
A little.
[RIMURU sighs]
That really ticked me off.
But the guy's a minister.
So I can't let my short fuse
screw things up
for Kaijin and this bar.
[GREAT SAGE]
Fruit wine.
Alcohol content
is seven percent.
[RIMURU] Thank you, Great Sage,
but this isn't the time.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-[groans]
[ALL gasp]
Hey, Vesta.
Just because that monster
is more polite than you are
doesn't mean I'm willing
to let your insults slide.
You... You brute.
How dare you talk to a minister
in such a manner?
Shut up!
-Kaijin.
-Go easy on him.
[RIMURU] Not in the face.
Aim for the body!
[shudders]
[grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[RIMURU] Was it a good idea
to punch a minister?
I don't want you
to get into any trouble.
[KAIJIN]
Hey, Rimuru.
You said you needed
some skilled artisans, right?
Think you can settle for me?
[RIMURU gasps]
Really?!
I don't need to settle
if I have you!
I'd be thrilled for you to help.
Welcome aboard!
Hmm.
[RIMURU]
But this isn't a fairy tale,
so things rarely
work out so smoothly.
Come on now, bro.
Just what the heck
were you thinking?
Hmph!
He had it coming.
That moron poured his drink
all over Rimuru,
and I decided it would be best
to teach him a little lesson.
A lesson, huh?
Look, you know you can't go
around assaulting a minister.
Hmph.
[RIMURU groans, sighs]
I don't have a choice here.
You broke the law.
I have to take you into custody.
You'll be detained
in the guardhouse
until the start
of your trial.
Guard.
Sorry about this,
it's not personal.
♪
[RIMURU]
Trial?
[groaning]
[exhales]
[inhales]
You've been asleep
this whole time?!
[sighs]
None of this would have happened
if I had just controlled
my temper.
What's worse is
I got you guys involved.
Sorry.
Hey, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Seriously, there's nothing
to even apologize for.
Mm-hmm.
[RIMURU]
Say something!
Your brother said
something about a trial.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Besides, it'll likely
end with a fine.
We won't get executed
or anything.
[laughing]
[RIMURU]
I'm glad you can laugh.
Still, is there a reason
why that Minister Vesta guy
seems to have it out for you?
Hmm.
You see,
I used to work under this
nation's king, Gazel Dwargo.
I served as a captain
back in the palace,
over one of the seven orders
of royal knights.
At the time,
Vesta was assisting me
as my second-in-command.
He was the son of a marquis,
and I came from
a family of peasants.
I'm sure it infuriated him.
Even back in those days,
we clashed constantly.
And then...
[inaudible]
[crackling]
-[yelling]
-[gasping]
[KAIJIN]
One of the projects
that Vesta had been
under pressure to complete,
the Magisoldier Project...
went up in smoke.
Naturally, Vesta used me
as a scapegoat
for the project's failure.
He even bribed my forces,
using them to present
a false testimony.
So I had no choice
but to accept responsibility
and quit the force.
These days,
he still has a grudge against me
and tries to make
unreasonable demands
at every opportunity.
That's what the sword thing
was about, too.
[RIMURU]
What a pathetic creep.
You're not wrong.
Still though,
if I'm being honest,
I really don't think
he's that bad a guy.
He and I had different ideas,
but he's a hard worker
and passionate
about his research.
The pressure he felt
to complete that project
came from his desire
to please the king.
Me leaving this town
might be good for him,
perhaps he'll wise up
and move on with life.
[RIMURU]
We can only hope.
Hmm. On that note, Rimuru,
thanks for having me on board.
[RIMURU]
Yeah.
[GARM]
Now hold on a second.
If you want Kaijin,
then you gotta take us, too.
Hmm?
He's right.
Anywhere Kaijin goes,
we'll follow.
We're a package.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Mm-hmm.
[RIMURU]
Figures.
Hmm.
Wow, you guys.
Well, Rimuru?
Would we get in your way
too much if we tagged along?
[RIMURU] Ha! I suppose I could
put up with you three.
But get ready, 'cause I'm gonna
work you to the bone!
-[BOTH] Right.
-Mm-hmm.
[ALL laughing]
[snoring]
[RIMURU]
Interesting.
He doesn't make much sound
even when he's asleep.
[exhales]
Uh... Huh?
-[RIMURU] Huh?
-Uh, my lord?
Did something bad happen?
[RIMURU] I can't believe
he's just now noticed.
We've got some
important things to do.
Is it cool if you hang out here?
Huh?
I mean, if you wanna get out,
you should just call
your Tempest Wolf partner
or something.
Uh, hey, that's no fair!
[RIMURU]
Don't worry.
I probably won't forget to come
back for you when we're done.
[mumbling]
[RIMURU sighs]
Well, I don't wanna
drag Gobta into this trial
when he wasn't even involved.
♪
His Majesty, Gazel Dwargo,
will now enter.
♪
[groaning]
[sighs]
[RIMURU narrating] The judge
presiding over Rimuru's party
is the Hero King
of the Dwarves, Gazel Dwargo.
Check out that guy's aura.
He's a beast!
No way I'd mess with him.
Everyone, we will now
begin the trial.
You may all rise.
[RIMURU]
This is me rising.
In the Armed Nation of Dwargon,
no one is allowed
to speak during a trial
without the king's
express permission.
For that reason,
a proxy is assigned
to speak for the defense.
In conclusion, Minister Vesta
was minding his own business
at the night club,
enjoying his drink.
Kaijin and his crew
entered the establishment,
and they assaulted
the minister.
Such boorish behavior must not
be tolerated in our city.
Looks like he's been bought.
[RIMURU]
This sucks.
The guy is supposed to be
defending our case.
Also, what's up with
all the extra bandages on Vesta?
And everything
you just stated is true?
Yes.
Beyond a shadow of a doubt.
King Gazel, now that you've
heard the proxy's testimony,
I request that you pass
your strictest judgment
upon these vagrants.
[RIMURU]
Kaijin said he thought
that Vesta wasn't
a bad guy deep down,
but I gotta disagree
on this one.
Please, sir.
[gavel pounding]
[ANNOUNCER] I will now deliver
the final verdict.
[RIMURU] Somehow I doubt
we'll get away
with just a measly fine.
I've got a really bad feeling.
First off,
Kaijin, the main offender.
You are hereby sentenced
to 20 years
-of forced labor in the mines.
-[RIMURU gasps]
Next, I shall sentence
his accomplices.
They will also serve time
doing forced labor,
for the next ten years.
[RIMURU]
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
[ANNOUNCER] That is all,
the court is now adjourned.
[RIMURU]
Whoa. What just happened?
-[GAZEL] Wait.
-Hmm?
[BOTH gasp]
It's been a while, Kaijn.
Have you been well?
Sir.
[ANNOUNCER]
Speak, Kaijin.
Answer his majesty.
[KAIJIN]
Yes, I have been well, my lord,
and I am relieved to see that
you are also in good health.
That's good to hear.
Are you at all interested
in returning to my ranks?
[gasps]
♪
Forgive me, Your Majesty,
but I have already
sworn myself to a master.
My word, and my oath
are the greatest treasures
I own.
And that's why,
I could never do anything
to forsake them,
even if you tried
to order me to do so.
[GUARD]
Insolence!
[RIMURU]
Whoa! Seriously?
♪
Right. I see.
I will pass my judgment.
Kaijin and his companions
are hereby exiled
from this land.
That is my verdict.
Disappear from my sight at once.
[RIMURU sighs]
Exile I can totally handle.
Still, he seems a little a down.
[sobbing]
[ANNOUNCER]
This court is now adjourned.
[door closes]
Right then, Vesta,
is there anything
you wish to say to me?
Uh, me, sir?
Well, I...
No. Nothing.
How unfortunate.
I am saddened by the fact
that I have lost
what I thought to be
a loyal retainer.
But how can you say
such a thing?
Kaijin, he...
He turned you down.
He swore his allegiance
to a slime monster.
He was never loyal to you,
he cares only for himself.
That's quite enough.
I fear you've
misunderstood me, Vesta.
[gasps]
Kaijin isn't the loyal retainer
I've lost.
No.
[shudders]
[GAZEL] Once upon a time,
I had great hopes for you.
I waited for years
after the failure
of the Magisoldier.
I wanted the truth,
but I'm tired of waiting.
Uh, please, sir.
Your Majesty, I swear.
It's too late for excuses.
Look what he has.
[VESTA gasps]
[GAZEL]
Do you know what that is?
It's a potion, a draft
of complete recovery,
made from hipokute herbs.
[VESTA]
It can't be.
Even with the most advanced
of dwarven techniques,
a potion can only achieve
98 percent recovery at the most.
How is this possible?
We received it as a gift,
from that slime.
[gasps]
Now because of your actions,
we've severed our relationship
with that monster.
Are you sure there's nothing
you'd like to say to me?
[shudders]
No, sir.
I have nothing to say.
♪
All I wanted was to be
useful to you somehow.
Ever since I first saw you
when I was but a young boy.
It has always been my dream.
And yet I...
I've failed to do just that.
All because I envied Kaijin.
Or was it something else?
For betraying
your great expectations,
I beg your forgiveness.
[sobbing]
[GAZEL] Vesta, never
show yourself to me again.
However, I do have
one last thing
I'd like to say
before you leave.
Thank you for your work.
[VESTA sobbing]
This is it.
Take care of yourself.
Sorry for all the trouble.
You take care, too.
Hmm.
Listen, Rimuru,
look after my bro.
[RIMURU] Don't you worry.
I'll only work him to death.
[scoffs]
Now then, by order
of His Majesty,
Kaijin and his companions have
been exiled from this country.
You are to leave here at once.
[RIMURU]
So, uh, shall we go?
My friends are waiting for us
in the forest.
Yeah.
[RIMURU narrating]
Despite all that happened,
Rimuru was able
to achieve his goal
of recruiting artisans
for the Goblin Village.
What's more, he managed to hire
the most skilled artisans
that Dwargon had to offer.
♪
Have you apprehended the proxy?
-Punish him severely.
-[DARK AGENT] Yes, sir.
And I want you to observe
that slime's movements.
It is unthinkable that we have
released such a monster.
Do not allow yourself
to be seen.
-No matter what.
-[DARK AGENT] Yes, sir.
That slime is too powerful.
Its strength is on par
with the Storm Dragon Veldora.
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time, "Shizu."