♪
[RIMURU] After we defeated
Demon Lord Geld,
we held a meeting that included
representatives from each race.
We needed to discuss
what would happen next.
Well, then,
Chairman Rimuru Tempest,
would you like to start?
[RIMURU]
Uh...
[chuckles]
[RIMURU groaning nervously]
[RIMURU] So, I've never really
done this kinda thing before.
I'm just gonna say
what's on my mind.
I'd like for you to reserve
your judgment until I'm done.
First things first.
I don't plan on
charging the orcs
with any sort of crimes.
[ORCS gasp]
[RIMURU] I know this may upset
the lizardmen
who lost the most men,
but hear me out.
This all started
because the orcs
were literally starving.
Anyone of any race might have
made the same choices
if they found themselves
in the same situation.
Of course, that's just
my personal opinion.
All right.
Is there anything else
you would like to add to that?
[RIMURU] I've taken all of
the orcs' sins upon myself.
So direct your complaints to me.
No. We can't allow that.
Such a burden isn't fair to you.
[RIMURU] Too bad.
I promised Demon Lord Geld.
[gasps]
I see, then.
Still, I feel as though
your decision
is somewhat unfair
to the rest of us.
[RIMURU] Yeah.
I can understand why
you wouldn't be cool with it.
Well, there is one
undisputable rule
all monsters follow.
"Survival of the fittest."
This is the way things
have always worked for our kind.
[RIMURU] You guys lost your home
because of this mess.
Don't you have any complaints?
I would be lying
if I said we didn't.
But despite them,
we will not let it happen again.
[RIMURU]
Right.
Very well, I suppose
you make a valid point.
Regarding this matter,
I do have an additional question
I'd like to ask.
[RIMURU]
Go on.
What do you intend to do
with the orcs?
[sighs]
You've already said that you
don't want to charge them
with any crimes,
but does that also mean
you're willing to accept
all their survivors?
[ORCS]
Hmm.
[RIMURU]
Even after the battle,
there are still
150,000 orcs,
which is a lot.
Listen, I know this might
be kind of a long shot,
but what do you guys think
about us all working together?
How so?
Just what do you mean?
[ORC A]
Hmm?
[RIMURU]
The lizardmen will share
their clean water source
and fish from the lake.
The goblins can offer housing.
And our town can provide them
with processed goods.
And in return for those things,
the orcs will agree
to contribute their labor.
[ORCS gasp]
[RIMURU] All the races
within the Great Forest of Jura
will form an alliance
which will be
mutually beneficial.
Wouldn't it be cool
if we built a nation
where all monsters
could coexist?
Wait, but that would mean
you want us orcs
to be a part
of your alliance, right?
[RIMURU] No offense,
but what are your other options?
A little labor and you've got
a place to live.
No lazy bums allowed.
[ORCS gasp]
[ORCS]
Right!
[ORC A]
Of course. We'll work hard.
In fact, we'll devote
our whole lives to helping.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
[CHIEFTAIN chuckles]
Well, then, we look forward
to working with you.
[RIMURU] Does that sound
good to you, Treyni?
[TREYNI]
It certainly does.
And the dryads will offer
our protection,
as well as the bounty
of the forest.
Which means we should be capable
of alleviating the orc's hunger.
[ORCS gasp]
Now...
as caretaker of the forest,
I, Treyni,
shall make a new proclamation.
I hereby appoint Rimuru Tempest
as the chancellor
of the Great Forest of Jura.
[RIMURU]
Chancellor?
The Jura Forest Alliance
is now formed.
Founded by Rimuru himself,
our new Chancellor.
[RIMURU]
Wait, uh, hold on.
Man, how the heck did I end up
as the chancellor?
Shouldn't that be Treyni's job?
And what's worse, it looks like
it's too late
to try and back out.
Fine, I guess I can do it.
Okay, then,
as your new Slime Chancellor,
I'm counting on all of you!
[ALL]
Yes, sir.
[RIMURU] There you have it,
that's how I, a humble slime,
somehow managed to establish
the Jura Forest Alliance.
Can I help you?
Even if it is
"survival of the fittest,"
hate is not an emotion
that can be forgotten so easily.
For what we did,
how we destroyed your village...
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
And I know that the request
I'm about to make
is a selfish one, but please,
I ask that you take my head
as penance
and have mercy
on my people.
[breathing heavily]
When the battle was over,
we told Lord Rimuru
that we wanted
to keep serving him,
so he gave us official titles.
I am a Samurai,
that's Lord Rimuru's
personal bodyguard
and his secretary.
[BENIMARU]
Hakurou is an instructor.
Souei is a spy.
The others, Shuna and Kurobe,
also have titles.
While I have the title
of Samurai General.
I'm in charge
of military affairs.
Now that I hold
such a crucial position,
it would be wrong of me
to rob us of a capable warrior.
-[footsteps receding]
-Huh?
♪
[BENIMARU] I will show no mercy
to any of those
who would harm Lord Rimuru.
But if you join the alliance,
then you and I are not enemies.
I will never wrong him, sir.
He is responsible
for saving my people.
I just want to serve him,
and I'd never bear him ill will.
[BENIMARU]
Excellent.
That means we're fellow servants
under Lord Rimuru.
Do your very best
to serve our master,
and I'll accept that
as your apology.
I swear on my father
King Geld's name.
[RIMURU] Benimaru sure is
a gracious dude.
I could learn
something from him.
Also, I should give
that guy a name,
since he'll be the new leader
of the orcs.
In hopes that you inherit
the wishes
of the late Orc Disaster
and your former king,
I'm naming you "Geld."
Yes, sir!
[RIMURU] I'm trusting you
to lead the orcs well.
Right.
[yells]
[RIMURU] The new orc ruler,
Geld, evolved into the Orc King.
After that,
I spent the next ten days
naming all 150,000 orcs.
Obviously, that was followed up
with a mandatory nap
due to magicule loss.
I also decided to name
the lizardman chieftain,
who is now known as "Abiru."
The Chieftain's son, Gabiru,
was charged with
the crime of treason.
[GABIRU] I'll surely receive
the death penalty.
It's fair.
And the only way
to set a proper example.
However, I do have
a single regret.
If I could do one more thing,
I'd ask him
why he saved my life.
Why me?
I'm just a worthless fool.
[ABIRU]
Raise your head.
I'm now ready to deliver
the verdict.
[GABIRU]
No matter what, I'm determined
to accept the death penalty
with grace.
For your crimes, I'm exiling you
from our clan.
And you are forbidden to ever
call yourself a lizardman again.
You are to leave here
immediately.
[GABIRU]
Wait. Seriously?!
[GABIRU grunts]
You forgot this. Take it.
[GABIRU gasps]
♪
[LIZARDMAN 2 laughs]
Sir Gabiru!
-Sir Gabiru!
-Hey!
Thank goodness,
we've been waiting for you.
Yeah.
What took you so long?
We were starting to worry.
Uh, I'm not even sure
why you're here.
You must be aware I was exiled.
Well, sure, but if
you're exiled, then we are, too.
That is true.
[voice breaking]
You guys...
are all idiots!
[GABIRU sniffles]
Not to mention
you're completely hopeless!
Fine then, I guess I'll just
have to look after you.
Follow me, men,
to a brighter future!
Whew. Sounds good.
-Hooray! [laughs]
-Let's go!
[LAPLACE] After all the trouble
you went to set that up,
it must drive you bonkers
that a new Demon Lord
wasn't born.
[MAN]
Perhaps a little.
Still though,
it was an amazing spectacle.
And that Slime,
what shall I do with it?
[LAPLACE] Sounds like you have
plans to make.
Well, should you
ever need a hand,
I'll lend you one for cheap,
Demon Lord Clayman.
[chuckles]
[RIMURU] Three months after
the downfall of the Orc Lord,
the orcs, who had
evolved into high orcs,
were thriving under Kaijin
and the other dwarves'
expert tutelage.
They were now valuable members
of the community.
[RIMURU] Mm-hmm! The houses
are turning out nicely.
Everyone has clothes and tools.
But the best part is,
our bangin' aqueduct!
We've got flushing toilets,
clean water and sewage systems!
We're even building roads.
Guess my years
in general contracting
have paid off.
These roads will be awesome
when we start doing
commerce and stuff.
And the bath I requested
is almost finished.
Oh, man, I can't wait!
Pretty cool, huh, Ranga?
Everyone has worked together
and now our little village
is a thriving haven
for monsters everywhere.
[RANGA] Yes.
It is truly magnificent, master.
[RIMURU]
Mm-hmm.
Our town was almost finished.
Soon we'd have a peaceful place
to call home.
Of course life rarely goes
the way we plan.
Lord Rimuru,
there's an emergency.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
♪
[SOUEI] The sky is filled
with Pegasus Knights,
and they're heading our way.
[RIMURU]
What?
♪
Hmm.
My King,
what did the letter say?
[GAZEL]
The Orc Lord was defeated.
It seems the war has ended.
It's over?
The remaining 150,000 orcs
surrendered their arms
and have now scattered.
What's more, they've all
evolved into high orcs.
That can't be.
[GAZEL] The message reported
that several superior majin
participated in the battle.
It might be presumptuous of me,
but I assume they are
all serving that Slime.
A Slime capable of ruling majin
and causing monsters to evolve.
How troublesome.
If this matter
is not handled with care,
then the nation may fall.
I will go visit this Slime.
If nothing else, I would like to
appraise it's worth myself.
♪
[panting]
[SHION gasps]
Hmm. It's him.
[RIMURU]
The hero king of the dwarves.
Gazel Dwargo.
Well, Lord Rimuru,
what should we do?
[RIMURU] I'd like to avoid
a fight, if possible.
No worries, my lord.
You want me to destroy them?
[RIMURU sighs]
[RIMURU] If this goes south,
I want you to evacuate the town.
We can buy time
while everyone else escapes.
Right.
[KAIJIN panting]
It's good to see you,
Your Majesty.
Have you been
doing well, Kaijin?
Yes.
The Slime.
[RIMURU]
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name's Rimuru.
While I am a slime, I'd rather
you didn't call me that.
Because I'm also the chancellor
of the Jura Forest Alliance.
Obviously this isn't
my actual form,
but it should at least
make talking easier.
So, what can I do for you?
I'll get straight to the point.
You see, I'm here to determine
your worth.
Meaning?
[GAZEL]
I'll judge you.
Using nothing
but the steel of my weapon.
[RIMURU gasps]
[GAZEL]
If you insist on boasting
about being
chancellor of this forest,
then it's up to me and my sword
to put you in your place.
Unless that toy on your hip
is just a decoration,
you had better
accept my challenge.
Please, sir, don't do this.
[scoffs]
Would a fight not be
the most direct way
to settle this dispute?
All right.
Have it your way, then.
But I'll make you regret
accusing me of bragging.
♪
[GAZEL]
If you can defend
against my entire chain
of attacks,
I'll declare you the winner.
[RIMURU gasps]
[GAZEL]
However, I should warn you
that in addition
to being a king,
I am also a master swordsman.
Got it.
[wind whooshing]
Very well. Then I shall serve
as witness to this contest.
It can't be. A dryad?
[GAZEL chuckles]
I suppose I should apologize
for accusing you of boasting.
I think I have
a better understanding
of what's going on now.
Yeah?
But regardless of that,
I still need to evaluate
your true nature.
Aww.
Now that we have a witness
for our battle,
you and I are ready
to cross swords.
Fine then, bring it on.
But after I win,
you'd better be prepared
to explain your real reason
for coming here.
[laughs]
If you somehow do,
I'll give you an answer.
Begin.
♪
And here I thought you'd be
more powerful, Rimuru.
Bite me.
Wait until I start taking
this seriously, King Gazel.
[yelling]
[RIMURU]
Man, he really is a beast.
But I can't exactly afford
to lose this contest.
[scoffs]
[RIMURU]
Wait, that stance.
Here I come, Rimuru.
Haze: Thunder of Heaven
and Earth!
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
The next strike is above!
[grunting]
[GAZEL]
Hmm.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
I can't believe
you blocked my attack.
Huh?
Enough.
The winner is Rimuru Tempest.
Uh...
Now that we've battled,
I know the truth.
It's obvious that you are not
a malicious being.
-[ALL] Mm-hmm.
-[RIMURU sighs]
No flipping duh.
I have to admit it,
I'm impressed that you
saw through my Haze:
Thunder of Heaven
and Earth attack.
You're an excellent fighter,
Rimuru.
It was more luck than anything.
It just so happens
my master uses that move
all the time in training,
so I'm used to it.
Pretty crazy, huh?
He does?
Hold on.
Who did you say your master was?
[gasps]
[laughs]
That was excellent work,
Lord Rimuru.
You're the Savant.
You don't look anything
like the little boy
I found lost in the forest,
you're much bigger now.
Oh. Do forgive me, King Gazel.
I have to admit I'm overjoyed
to see that you have surpassed
my own skill with the sword.
It's an honor to receive
such a huge compliment.
[RIMURU]
Hakurou was his master?
I'm pretty surprised at how
connected everyone can be,
even in a world like this one.
-[indistinct conversations]
-[laughter]
I see.
This was about the Orc Lord.
You wanted to know
who was behind his downfall.
Yes, and to see whether
they were friends or enemies.
Now you understand.
Rimuru, may I ask something?
Sure.
Would you be interested
in entering a treaty with me?
Huh?
[GAZEL]
If you were to gain control
of everything in this forest
and its surrounding areas,
it's possible you could obtain
wealth and power surpassing
that of my own nation.
And that's why,
it's imperative
that you gain support
from another country.
Don't get me wrong,
that'd be awesome, but...
It's just...
Are you really okay
with acknowledging
our monster town
as its own nation?
That's a pretty big deal,
you know?
I do, and I accept it.
This deal would benefit
both our parties.
In this event,
we all stand to profit.
[RIMURU sighs]
Not like I can really refuse.
Right, consider it a deal.
Thank you.
So, all that's left is for you
to pick a name for your nation.
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
Cool, I'm just naming a nation.
No pressure or anything!
Let's see.
Maybe I can combine
the "Forest of Jura"
and "Rimuru Tempest" somehow.
It's the
Jura Tempest Federation.
Ah, that's an excellent choice
for a name.
-[BENIMARU chuckles]
-That's our Lord Rimuru.
Hold on.
If this is the
Jura Tempest Federation,
then we have to name our town
Rimuru after our lord.
[gasps]
It'll be the nation's capital.
[RIMURU]
Hang on.
That's kinda embarrassi--
What a fantastic idea.
No other name would do.
Right, I agree.
No one here could possibly
object to that name.
[RIMURU]
Except me.
It sounds like it's settled.
[RIMURU]
Yeah.
In that moment,
A new nation was born,
and the names
"Jura Tempest Federation"
and "Capital City Rimuru"
were engraved into history
for the first time.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Demon Lord Milim Attacks."