♪
[RIMURU] The development
of the goblin village
continued to progress.
Kaijin and the three
dwarf brothers,
Garm, Myrd and Dord,
worked together to make clothing
and tools for everyone.
The homes were also
coming along nicely.
Meanwhile, the goblin lords
working under Rigurd
established a system
for ruling the village.
[inaudible]
[RIMURU]
Everything's going great.
I don't even
have to be that bossy
because they all
just do their jobs.
Makes life easier for me.
Which is good, since I have
some personal matters
I need to take care of.
Huh? [gasps]
Perfect! I'm all alone.
[straining]
There, good as new.
Shizu, I promise to treasure
this keepsake of you.
Now, then.
[laughing]
Transform!
♪
Huh.
Thanks to Mimic,
I have a real human body.
I can't believe it.
I've missed this.
Vision.
Hearing.
[indistinct chatter in distance]
Well, that sucks.
I think my hearing as a slime
is actually better,
but I wonder why.
Is it because of Magic Sense?
Okay.
Hey, Great Sage,
since I ate Ifrit,
can I use Body Double?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
All of Ifrit's skills,
including Body Double,
have been analyzed.
That's awesome! Right.
Let's try that sucker out.
Body Double!
[gasps]
Aw, man. I look like Shizu.
There's no remnants
of my former manliness.
I sure am a beautiful... dude?
Dudette?
[RIMURU]
Not to sound like a total perv,
but I'd like to know
what sex my human body is.
Though, I think I have a pretty
good idea of what it might be.
But there's only one way
to know for sure.
[groans]
Hey, diddle, diddle,
there is no fiddle.
Whoa, hold the phone.
I don't think I'm a lady either.
I'm sexless!
Well, it's not like I really had
a gender as a slime anyway.
Huh? Wait a second.
When I took
my human form earlier,
I didn't see
any of that black mist.
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
When using Mimic to assume
a form larger than yourself,
black mist produced
by magicule consumption
makes up the difference.
So that means I could totally
create an adult form, too!
Right!
Whoa! Can it be more manly?
♪
[RIMURU]
Hey, looking good, champ.
Okay, now make it more feminine.
Cool! Wait!
Stop! Stop! Never mind.
[panting]
Figures.
If I make the form look female,
I feel kinda like
I'm peeping on Shizu a bit.
That concludes my report, sir.
[RIMURU] Good. It sounds like
things are running smoothly.
-Oh, also...
-[RIMURU] Huh?
About food, I guess you won't be
needing any, as usual?
Nah. It'd just be a waste seeing
as I don't have any taste buds.
[gasps]
Whoa!
-Rigurd!
-Yes?
I've decided
that starting today,
I'd like to eat with you guys.
Truly, sir?
If you want, we could prepare
a lavish feast for you.
Okay. Please do so.
[RIGURD]
Right.
[RIMURU]
This is awesome!
My human form comes
equipped with taste buds.
I'm gonna eat like
nobody's business.
I wonder what'll
be on the menu.
Meat, maybe? I'm all about that.
Oh, man, rice sounds good, too.
But I haven't seen
any rice plants.
I should look for some.
Then maybe we could
sow some fields.
[gasps]
Lord Rimuru.
[RIMURU] Thanks for always
hunting for us, Rigur.
It is my honor, sir.
We were just on our way
to the forest now.
They're planning
to have a feast tonight.
Bring back
something tasty, okay?
So, does that mean
you're gonna eat with us?
Sure am.
This body has taste buds
and I'm anxious to use them.
Ohh!
If you eat a lot, do you think
your boobs will grow in?
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
[GOBTA grunting]
Uh... I'm sorry.
I promise to make sure
Gobta is strictly disciplined.
Anyway, I'll prepare some
gourmet bulldeer for the feast.
Huh?
[mooing]
Cool! Sounds good.
[RIGUR]
Leave it to me.
A lot of magical beasts
have been emerging
from the forest lately.
So there's ample prey.
Huh? Why are they coming out?
Well, it's common for animals
to move to a new place
when the environment changes.
I doubt it's anything
worth worrying about.
Sure.
Hmm.
♪
[RANGA]
How may I serve you, master?
Ranga, go into the forest
with Rigur's team.
I don't think
anything'll happen,
but I'd feel better
if you were there.
[RANGA] As you wish.
You can count on me.
There's no need
for reservation, Rigur.
I'll keep you safe.
[RIMURU]
Way to sound super cool, Ranga!
The tail wagging
kinda ruins it, though.
♪
[RIMURU]
Afterward, I paid a visit
to the cave
where Veldora had been sealed.
I wanted to test out
my new Unique Skill.
"Degenerate" was something
I received from Shizu.
And I wanted to try it
where no one would get hurt.
Regardless of the impression
the name "Degenerate" left,
the skill had been
important to Shizu,
which also made it
precious to me.
It's pretty cool.
It uses
unification and separation
to merge skills together,
allowing them to evolve
into new skills.
So basically,
she was able to use it
to gain a bunch
of new abilities.
Including...
♪
Whoa. What's this?
[GREAT SAGE] It is
an Extra Skill, Black Flame.
I see. I should be careful
with this, too.
[whooshing]
Still though,
I only have these things
because of Shizu.
She said this mask has the power
to suppress magic, right?
Well, how's this?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
The aura you were
previously emitting
has been completely erased.
In this state, you would be
perceived as a regular human.
[RIMURU]
Word.
I should probably wear this
when I go to new places, then.
Lookin' slick.
[GREAT SAGE]
Uh-huh.
[RIMURU]
Gee, thanks a lot.
-[RANGA] Lord Rimuru!
-[RIMURU gasps]
[GREAT SAGE] Receiving
Thought Communication
from Ranga.
Vocal tone indicates
it is a request for aid.
♪
[panting]
[grunting]
[groaning]
[GOBTA]
No, I'm too young to die!
-Ow. Ow. Ow!
-[RIMURU] What happened?
I got cut real bad!
-Am I gonna die like this?
-Calm down, it's not deep.
[RIMURU gasps]
-[groaning]
-[RIMURU] Who are they?
Wait. Lord Rimuru, it's you?
Did you come all the way
out here just to help us?
[RIMURU]
Yep, that's right.
And since you're so lively,
I guess you don't need a potion.
[GOBTA]
Uh... No. I still want one.
I'm sorry I joked
about your boobs earlier.
[grunts, gasps]
Wow, thanks a lot, sir!
-[RANGA howling]
-[RIMURU gasps]
♪
[grunts]
[RIMURU]
Ranga.
[RANGA]
Master, forgive me.
After you sent me
to protect them...
[clanging]
[grunting]
[RIMURU]
Rigur, retreat.
[grunts]
[grunts, pants]
[RIGUR]
Lord Rimuru, I'm so sorry.
[RIMURU] Don't worry.
Leave them to me.
You just get some rest.
You're too kind, my lord.
[RIMURU] Ranga, what happened to
the rest of the hunting party?
[RANGA] Oh. They've been put
to sleep with magic.
The pink-haired one
is responsible for it.
♪
[RIMURU]
Magic, huh?
Looks like these guys
are gonna be trouble.
I'm so sorry, sir.
I never expected
that we would run into ogres.
[RIMURU]
Ogres?
The ones in video games
are always so jacked.
[roaring]
[RIMURU] But these guys and gals
look way different.
They're even wearing armor.
That guy's sword looks
kind of like a katana.
Six of them in all.
Listen up.
I don't know what happened,
but we don't want any trouble.
Would you be willing
to talk this out?
They're obviously very strong,
and yet Gobta and Rigur
weren't fatally wounded.
In fact, most of our team
was only put to sleep.
There must be a reason for that.
Looks like I'll have to be
the grown-up here
and fix things.
[MAN]
Stop messing around, majin.
-Show us who you really are.
-[RIMURU] Huh?
[RIMURU] Whoa, hold up.
What did you just call me?
Enslaving monsters is not a feat
that a mere human could
accomplish without using magic.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Enough trickery!
Hiding your appearance
and aura won't save you.
Reveal your true identity.
It appears the mastermind
has come to us.
Should make things easier.
[RIMURU]
What?!
But my true identity
is just a squishy,
yet adorable,
little slime monster!
[RIMURU]
You've got the wrong idea.
[scoffs]
We have no intention
of listening to your lies.
The mask you wear
has already told us the truth.
[RIMURU]
Huh? My mask?
Okay, now I know
this is a misunderstanding.
This is just a keepsake
from a friend.
[gasps]
[MAN]
I'll hear no more!
I will avenge
my fallen brethren,
even if it means
taking your head.
Today you will die,
evil pig leader!
[RANGA]
What should we do?
[RIMURU]
Good question.
You take care
of the pink-haired one.
[RANGA]
Yes, master.
-[RIMURU] Do not kill her.
-[RANGA] Sir?
[RIMURU] I think
there's more to all this.
So just run interference for me.
I'll take care of the rest.
[RANGA] But that would leave you
to fight five ogres by yourself.
[RIMURU] It'll be fine.
I don't plan on losing.
[RANGA] As expected
of my master. Leave it to me.
You underestimate us.
You are very brave,
or very stupid.
Regardless,
I'm happy to face you.
It should be a decent fight,
as well as your last!
[grunting]
[gasping]
[RIMURU]
Looks like you need a nap.
[groaning]
♪
[groans weakly]
[RIMURU] Sorry, but I saw you
coming with Magic Sense.
Holy hooters!
Wait, I swear that's not what
I meant when I said I saw you.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[RIMURU] I've never had a woman
fall so hard for me.
Just kidding.
♪
[clang]
[groaning]
-Whoa!
-Way to go, sir!
[RANGA growling]
[WOMAN]
He beat us that easily?
[RIMURU]
That's three down.
All right, who's next?
[OLD MAN]
Hmm.
The Centipede's
Paralysis Breath.
The Black Spider's
Sticky Steel Thread.
And the Armorsaurus' Body Armor.
[RIMURU gasps]
[OLD MAN] There's no telling
just how many skills
he may possess
from other monsters.
Do not let your guard down,
young master.
[RIMURU] That old guy was able
to name off my skills
and the monsters they came
from with one quick look?
I might need to play my cards
a little closer to my chest.
Can we stop this, already?
I'd still be interested
in talking things out.
Quiet! Enough, majin.
[RIMURU]
So, uh, is that a no?
I admit you're rather strong,
which only confirms
my suspicions.
[RIMURU]
Which is what?
That you are
obviously one of them.
Who's "them"?
[MAN] It is unthinkable
that we mighty ogres
would be defeated
by a bunch of lowly orcs.
[RIMURU] Orcs? Whoa, can we just
back up for a second?
Silence!
I know it was you and the work
of your majin comrades.
[RIMURU]
Uh, come again?
It was you!
[RIMURU] Listen, you've got
this all wrong.
[gasps]
Huh?
[OLD MAN] Hmm. I must be
getting slow in my old age.
I was certain
that I'd cut off your head.
[RIMURU]
What the heck?
Lord Rimuru!
Uh-oh, your arm.
[RANGA growling]
Master.
[RIMURU]
I'm fine.
Don't let your guard down.
He got past my Magic Sense
and broke through my Multilayer
Barrier and Body Armor?
[OLD MAN]
Next time, I won't miss.
It would appear you're driven
by sheer foolishness.
I must commend your ability to
remain calm after losing an arm.
However, your arrogance
will be your downfall.
I told you not to
underestimate us ogres.
Perhaps you'll be smarter
in your next life!
♪
-[gasps]
-Huh?
[RIMURU laughs]
You think chopping off
an arm will stop me?
Sheesh.
And you called me arrogant.
[grunts]
You will die here!
Ogre Flame!
♪
-[OLD MAN] Young master.
-Is he dead?
[gasps]
[RIMURU] What a shame.
Fire immunity, am I right?
I do have to give you credit.
I underestimated your abilities.
In return, I won't hold back.
[grunts]
[OLD MAN]
His aura's incredible.
Take it all in, boys.
♪
[gasps]
Huh? No way! That's impossible.
Normally a magic flame
would be produced
by the surrounding magicules.
But this flame is different,
it's powered by nothing
but his strength.
And the size of the flame
is reflecting the size
of his power.
Don't worry, the show's
not over yet, folks.
Because I'm just
getting started!
[gasps]
[groans]
Huh?
[electricity crackling]
[RIMURU]
Oops.
So much for keeping
my cards close to my chest, huh?
What now? Still wanna fight?
[grunts]
[RIMURU]
Good, he seems scared.
Come on, man,
just surrender already.
[OLD MAN] Sir, Please take
the princess and flee.
I shall end this.
Quiet, old man.
[OLD MAN sighs]
That's an intense flame.
I hate to admit it,
but it would appear
that we're no match for you.
That doesn't matter.
I refuse to run away.
As the leader of the powerful
ogre clan, I must stand proud.
I cannot leave until
I've avenged my slain brethren.
I must defeat you!
Even if I die,
I will fight to my last breath.
[OLD MAN] Young master,
it would be an old man's honor
to fight alongside you.
[RIMURU]
Seriously? Well, damn.
This bluff totally backfired.
[panting]
Brother, stop, I beg of you!
This man,
he may not be our enemy.
Out of my way!
-No!
-[gasps]
Why? He's a masked majin,
is he not?
He's just like the one
who attacked our village.
You saw the mask yourself.
Yes, but please,
we need to try
and think about this calmly.
It's true
that he's extremely powerful.
So why would he hire orcs?
Why use them to
indirectly attack our village?
It makes no sense.
Obviously, he's strong enough
to kill us by himself
if he wanted to.
Mm-hmm.
[WOMAN] There is no doubt
that he is different from us.
And he's strong,
but I truly believe
that he has no connection
to the attack.
[softly]
Huh? Hmm?
How about it, are you
more willing to talk now?
I'll just put this away.
Tell us who you are.
Really.
Me? I'm just a friendly slime.
Seriously?
Yeah. Rimuru the Slime.
[BOTH gasp]
So it's true, then.
[RIMURU] As I said, this mask
is a keepsake from a friend.
You're welcome to look at it
and see if it's the same one
the person who attacked
your village used.
Very well.
It does seem similar, but...
[WOMAN] This one has some kind
of magic suppression power.
[OLD MAN]
The majin who attacked back then
wasn't doing anything
to conceal their aura.
So then...
forgive us.
We were too quick to judge
and behaved rashly.
Please accept my apology.
[RIMURU]
Sure, it's all good.
Yowza!
For a minute there, things
were lookin' pretty hairy.
Well, we should probably
talk somewhere else.
Let's go back to our village.
You can join us there.
Wait. Are you sure?
[RIMURU] Yep. I'd like to hear
what happened to you.
But we attacked you
and wounded your companions.
And we put the hurt
on some of yours.
But, hey, no one kicked
the bucket, so we're cool.
-I'm sorry I injured you.
-[GOBTA gasping]
[RIGUR chuckles]
[RIMURU] Besides, we're having
a huge feast today.
More people just means more fun.
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
[RIMURU] And so,
the battle which had begun
before we even knew why ended.
The ogre princess agreed
to reverse the sleep spell,
and all the goblins
and wolves woke up.
Rimuru healed everybody's wounds
with his potions,
and then the whole gang headed
back to the goblin village
to prepare for the big feast.
So, hey, what's your name?
Oh, I'm afraid
we do not possess names.
Of course. I forgot
that's a thing around here.
That's right. That's right.
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time, "The Orc Lord."