[inaudible]
[RIMURU] In hopes of saving
Shizu's students,
Rimuru took them
to the Dwelling of Spirits.
There they met the Queen
of the Spirits, Ramiris.
She agreed to help them
with their situation,
and the party set out to try
and summon superior spirits.
♪
[RIMURU]
What is this?
[RAMIRIS] The deepest part
of the Labyrinth,
the Dwelling of Spirits.
Kenya, Ryota, Chloe,
Alice, and Gale.
Game time.
[KIDS]
Yeah!
[RAMIRIS chuckles]
[RIMURU] Shizu, I hope
that you can somehow see this.
I promise you,
I will fulfill your final wish.
[RAMIRIS]
All right, listen.
Up there's the place
where you'll have to
call out for the spirits.
Call out?
Like talk to them.
Say you want their help
or that you wanna play.
And if any spirits show up,
then that means
they're interested in you.
But what if they don't come?
Of course they will.
Yeah, sure.
Right, Teach? It'll work out.
Will it really?
Yup, don't worry,
and if all else fails,
then we'll find a demon
to possess you instead.
Don't scare them
with your creepy face.
[RIMURU]
Who wants to go first?
Hey, Teach?
If this doesn't work out,
please take care of them.
Go.
I can't wait to see what kind of
spirit comes to play with you.
Right. Here goes.
[inhales]
♪
[BOTH gasp]
[GROUP gasps]
[RIMURU]
Well, something showed up,
but it looks like
they're only inferior spirits.
These small particles
have no free will.
They're just snippets
cut from a greater spirit
by Gale's prayer.
But we can use them
to make a new spirit.
Great Sage?
[GREAT SAGE]
Question.
Would you like to use Gluttony
to consume
and unify the spirits?
[RIMURU]
It's our only option.
Good job.
Keep on praying, Gale.
Huh?
♪
Hey, hold on!
You jerk.
Why'd you eat those spirits?
I have an idea. Just trust me.
Let's do it, Great Sage.
[GREAT SAGE]
Notice.
Using the Unique Skill
Degenerate.
Unification into
a Superior Spirit is complete.
[RIMURU]
Great!
[GREAT SAGE]
Its attribute is Earth.
Creating an artificial
personality. Success.
Unify the completed artificial
superior spirit of Earth
with Gale Gibson?
[RIMURU]
Yes.
♪
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
Okay, use Appraisal.
His rampant energy
is calming down.
He has control.
Now, as his body matures,
he should gradually acquire
some new skills and abilities.
Way to go, Great Sage.
[GREAT SAGE scoffs]
[RIMURU] Is it just me or do you
sound kind of smug right now?
[GREAT SAGE]
It's just you.
All right, it's over.
Nice job, Gale.
[GALE]
Huh?
You'll be okay.
The energy's contained.
You're good to go.
[GALE gasps]
Whoa, really?
Thank you so much!
Hey, no biggie.
It's all part of being
a good teacher, right?
[GALE chuckles softly]
-Yay!
-[RYOTA] Congrats, Gale!
-[ALICE] Awesome work!
-[CHLOE] That's wonderful!
[RANGA howls]
Don't get too carried away.
Save the celebrating
for when you're all done.
♪
[groans softly]
[RAMIRIS]
Hmm...
[GREAT SAGE]
Notice.
Using the Unique Skill
Degenerate.
Unification into
a Superior Spirit is complete.
Its attribute is space.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
[GREAT SAGE]
Unify the completed artificial
superior spirit of space
with Alice Rondo?
[RIMURU]
Yes.
♪
[KIDS groan]
All done. Way to go.
You'll be okay now.
[ALICE laughs softly]
Oh, wow, thanks.
[laughing]
[grunts]
'Kay.
Guess it's my turn to go.
[RIMURU gasps]
Wait, I haven't started praying.
Hold on. What's that?
Huh?
Hi. How are ya?
I'm doing great.
[RAMIRIS]
Hey! Who said you could
barge in here uninvited?
Oh, I just felt like
dropping in.
What is that thing?
-Uh, well--
-Hi there.
I'm a pure light spirit.
Nice to meet ya.
And unlike this teeny meanie
who went to the dark side,
I'm a sweet,
innocent spirit of light.
[RAMIRIS]
More like annoying!
Kenya, it looks like you managed
to summon
a superior light spirit.
Whoa. What?!
Oh, so your name's Kenya?
Mind if I call you Ken?
Anyway, I just felt somethin'
shinin' inside ya, Ken.
-You know, 'cause I'm light.
-[RAMIRIS groans]
Was that, like, a joke?
Funny, right?
Okay, I've decided
I'm gonna save you.
I'll take extra good care of you
till you're all grown up.
And who knows?
You might even grow up to be
an honest to goodness Hero.
-A Hero?
-There's no way that'll happen.
Whoa, did you hear
what it said?
Awesome.
-That would be something.
-[KENYA groaning]
Whoa.
-[RAMIRIS] It's in you.
-What?
Just like that, huh?
Uh, Teach?
Yeah?
Oh! It's fine.
Just like I planned!
[laughs]
Good job, kiddo.
Uh, really?
Right!
♪
[GREAT SAGE] Notice.
Attributes are water and wind.
Creation of
artificial superior spirit
of water and wind successful.
Unify it with Ryota Sekiguchi?
[RIMURU]
Yes.
Only one left.
I wanna tell you that I...
[RIMURU]
Hmm?
Huh?
The thing is, I, uh...
Well, Teach...
I love you.
I like you, too.
[CHLOE chuckles softly]
[RIMURU] What I wouldn't give
for you to wait another eight,
no, ten years to say that to me.
Couldn't get anyone to say it
in my old life.
Well, you ready?
Yes.
♪
-[explosion]
-[RIMURU gasps]
-[rumbling]
-What's that?
♪
[RIMURU]
That pressure.
It felt like
the sky crashed down on us.
-[explosion]
-[RAMIRIS screams]
♪
[RIMURU]
Uh... Is that a spirit?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
It is a spiritual body
equivalent to a superior spirit.
The being's energy level
is abnormal.
Its threshold is immeasurable.
♪
[RIMURU gasps]
[RIMURU]
What the...
No way! I won't let you.
Not in my house!
-Hey, what's going on?
-Just look!
You seriously can't tell?
She's dangerous.
And I would know that how?
Also, don't yell at me.
We'll talk la--
[gasps]
♪
It's in Chloe!
Now it's too late.
[RAMIRIS grunts]
Well, it's not my fault.
[RIMURU]
Use Appraisal.
It looks as though
that intense energy
has completely disappeared.
Good news is, she's stable.
I guess everything's okay.
Still, that was weird.
[CHLOE]
Uh...
What kinda spirit was that?
[RAMIRIS] Hey, don't ask me.
I don't have all the answers.
But I think maybe that thing
was born in the future.
What?
It's kinda like a spirit,
but it came from the future.
I know it sounds impossible,
but by choosing Chloe,
it's laid the foundation
for its own rebirth.
[CHLOE]
Huh?
It sounds crazy.
[grunts in frustration]
How do I explain it?
That thing's
mega powerful, okay?
Look, if it's born
in the future,
it's gonna be
major trouble for us.
I wonder if it had
the divine protection
from the Great Spirit of Time.
[RIMURU]
I am so lost.
Whatever.
As long as Chloe's okay,
that's all that matters.
No one knows what will happen
in the future,
so it's not worth
worrying about.
[CHLOE chuckles]
[RIMURU laughs softly]
Excellent work, Chloe.
It went just as planned.
You'll be safe
from danger now, okay?
[CHLOE]
Uh...
Wait, so all of that
was part of your plan?
Uh... Yes! Of course it was.
-[laughing]
-[howls]
[RAMIRIS]
There's not much we can do.
Now that it's inhabited her,
the situation
is out of my control.
It'll be fine.
I'm just glad that she's okay.
Thanks, Ramiris.
You saved
these children's lives today.
-Yes, thank you.
-[RAMIRIS] Uh...
[KIDS]
Thank you so very much.
[RANGA]
I'm grateful!
[RAMIRIS gasping]
[RAMIRIS] One thank you
is more than enough, okay?
[RIMURU] To think
she's really a Demon Lord.
This world is full of surprises.
[FAIRIES giggling]
♪
[laughing]
So cute!
[RIMURU]
I did it, Shizu.
Your students are safe.
And we all lived
happily ever after.
[laughs]
Psyche.
Actually, I still owed Ramiris
a replacement
for the golem
I kinda sorta destroyed.
♪
Of course the golem
was just a shell,
so then I had to summon
a demon to possess it.
And there would be
one last struggle.
But that's a story
for another time.
I can't thank you enough,
Rimuru.
[RIMURU chuckles]
No thanks necessary, my dude.
I'm just glad the kids are okay.
They should be able to lead
normal lives now, right?
Yes. It's highly unlikely
the nations
who abandoned them
will try to take them back.
And it'd violate
international law.
They would be making enemies
out of the Free Union
if they did try that.
[RIMURU] Are you planning
on giving the kids IDs
and making them
members of the Union?
Who knows?
It's not a bad idea
if that's what they want.
So it's certainly a possibility.
For right now, I'd like to
let them continue studying
at Freedom Academy and give them
a choice about their futures.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, that sounds cool.
They're in good hands.
I wanted to ask.
How did you pull it all off?
Like, how did you save them?
[RIMURU laughs]
That's a trade secret.
Some things are just
better off not knowing.
And while it probably doesn't
make up for not telling you,
here is a consolation prize.
[grunts]
[YUUKI]
This is awesome!
Thank you so much, Rimuru!
[KIDS laughing]
[indistinct playful chatter]
[KENYA]
Hey, wait for me!
-[RANGA grunts, pants]
-[KIDS laughing]
[ALICE]
We're coming!
[KIDS laughing]
♪
[RIMURU] So much has happened
since I came to this world.
♪
But now it's over.
They're safe.
All of our problems
are resolved.
[wind blowing]
Shizu, you can rest in peace.
[SHIZU'S VOICE]
Thank you, Mister Slime.
[MAN]
How could this happen?
After I was so close
to being summoned.
And then to have my own family
beat me to the punch.
Next time...
Next time I will not fail.
He will be the one
to lead me.
Perhaps he'll be able to show me
the truth of this world.
[laughing]
[KIDS crying]
Please, don't leave.
We'll miss you.
Stop that.
Teach has to go back home,
he can't stay with us.
That's right.
Just get going already!
-But I...
-[RIMURU sighs]
♪
They're all yours.
Yeah. I'll watch over them.
Teach, wait!
[crying]
[KENYA]
Chloe, you're such a crybaby!
Cut it out!
You're crying, too, Ken.
Nuh-uh! I'm sweating
from my eyeballs!
[CHLOE]
Don't leave. Stay here.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
I can't.
But it'll be okay.
What if I give you
this mask to keep?
[BOTH gasp]
I wanted him to give me that!
But he gave it to me.
Man, lucky!
That's not fair!
[RIMURU] Relax, I have gifts
for you guys, too.
[chuckles]
Whoa!
[laughs]
Aw, man, you look awesome!
Yeah, so do you.
These robes are amazing.
We look so cute!
My friend Shuna's really good
at sewing clothes and stuff.
So she made these
just for you.
That's cool!
Thanks so much.
[RIMURU]
Listen up.
No slacking off on your studies.
This isn't really goodbye.
I'm sure we'll all meet
again someday.
Ranga and I can visit
in our free time.
[RANGA] Be sure to dedicate
yourselves to studying,
even after we're gone.
Fine.
But you'd better not forget
to come and see us!
Also, maybe after
we all graduate,
we can come visit you
in your country.
Sure. Sounds good.
I know everyone in my city
will welcome you with open arms.
♪
-See ya!
-Safe travels!
-[ALICE] Take care now!
-[GALE] We'll see you later!
Take care, kids!
Goodbye.
[RANGA] Master, why did you give
Chloe your special mask?
Oh. To be honest,
I'm not really sure.
It sounds kinda weird, I know.
But in the end,
giving the mask to Chloe
felt like
the natural thing to do.
And I think it was for the best.
[RANGA]
I see.
[RIMURU] I bet
if Shizu could have chosen,
she would have preferred that
Chloe had it over me, anyway.
Plus, I'm sure
she'll take good care of it.
Maybe Chloe will follow
in Shizu's footsteps.
She could grow up
to be a Champion,
or maybe even a Hero.
[RANGA]
Perhaps.
[RANGA and RIMURU laugh]
Ranga?
[RANGA]
What is it, Master?
I'm ready to go home.
To our town.
Everyone's waiting.
♪
[howls]
[RIMURU]
There once was a middle-aged man
who lived a perfectly
ordinary life in Japan.
But then he was
stabbed to death,
and so he was reincarnated
in a new world.
He absorbed
the Storm Dragon Veldora,
as well as the body and will of
a powerful Champion named Shizu.
He overcame many challenges
and brought together
monsters of all races.
He built a nation and saved
children from an early grave.
His name is Rimuru Tempest.
And he is not
a bad slime. Slurp.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Extra: Black and a Mask."