Now I get it. But we're
not loaning Rock to you.
We're staying out of this one.
But why?! You can't!
Because your head maid is nuts.
She's on a crusade
against everyone's
favorite buddy, Uncle Sam.
And in my book,
that's bat-shit crazy.
Seems that way.
She's about to jump into
a cage match with the USA
and she's not gettin' out alive.
All the more reason.
Please. You need to help us.
Am I the only person in the
world who wants to save her?
We have to do something!
Fucking crybaby.
Did you come to
the asshole of the
world just to blubber?
Cry me a damn river,
no one gives a shit!
Maybe a superhero will swoop
down and come to the rescue!
That's enough!
Fabiola, it's okay.
We both know she's right.
No point in making
fools of ourselves.
We will continue to
search for her on our own.
Garcia, you've grown up a lot.
You're more like a man now.
Those are kind words, but
without Father and Roberta,
I've had no choice.
It's sad, but it's the truth.
I see. Is that it, Rock?
"I see...?" The thought of
throwing these two kids out on
the street breaks my heart
and I'm not just saying that.
You know what I'd like?
To send them both back safely
to their manor in Venezuela
while we take
care of this ourselves!
You'll help us?!
This isn't like you, Chang.
You never let us know
what you're really thinking.
Ha! Was I
overselling it, Dutch?
It's obvious that
the maid is gonna go
toe to toe with the U.S. Army.
I can't see that being
good for me or the city.
That's not our problem.
Keeping the peace is your job.
Cut the bullshit, Dutch.
In your line of work, Rock
can go anywhere in the city.
And he knows the territory.
Plus, he's the
safest bet because
he has a few less
enemies than the rest of you.
Even if they
hadn't asked for you, Rock,
you'd still be the right choice.
Friend, these kids need
your help. Don't let them down.
You say you
want to help the city,
and you want
that maid out of here
before things go to hell. So to
do that I need to help Garcia
and his friend here find Roberta
before she finds the Americans.
Is that it, Mr. Chang?
Anything else?
The plan is very simple, Rock.
I'd like some more time. I
really have to think about this.
Listen you two,
if he doesn't help you,
you need to get out of here
immediately. No arguments.
Listen to the
adults on this one.
Rock, at this rate
the boy's gonna be
a gray-haired old
man before he's twenty.
Wouldn't you agree?
See ya around, "Young Master."
Spare me the lost kitty routine.
I mean, come on, Rock. You
really think I'm gonna let you
work on this between jobs?
The problem is
you're in deep shit
if you do find that kitty cat.
Open the door
where she's been hiding
and that cat will leap out
and tear you a new asshole!
There's just one rule.
And as long as I'm your boss,
this isn't up for debate.
If that maid runs into the
U.S. Army before you find her,
you drop the job and
do it quick. Non-negotiable.
Well, whatta you know?
Just another simple
rule I have to follow.
You think he'll take the job?
That's the kind of man he is.
He's a rare individual in this
city. He still has his ideals.
Roanapur, a natural
gathering point
for criminal organizations...
The Hong Kong Triad,
Hotel Moscow, the Cosa Nostra,
the Columbian Cartel,
and countless others.
During the Second World War,
the Japanese dredged the harbor
to make Roanapur
into their naval base.
After the war, it became a
transit port for drug smugglers.
Now it's worse.
The city's like a rat's nest
stuffed with illegal contraband.
And you want me to save those
kids in a place like this?!
Think! Forget about
your self-doubts and think!
C'mon, you can do this! What
are the common factors here?
This is the source
of the drug trade
and this is the
mouth of the river.
Damn! You've backed yourself
into a corner
now figure this out!
No, I should simplify.
The Italians might not
involve themselves in this deal.
Not like the South Americans.
The Cartel has been
in this from the start.
Gustavo said HQ is
sending them soldiers.
FARC troops are coming here to
deal with the maid personally.
A three way fight between
the maid, the Americans,
and the Colombians.
Here in town.
It'll be a bloodbath!
I have a question for you.
Oh? Working on
your resignation letter?
You're being stubborn.
A little bit.
I remember you once said that
Balalaika owes you big time.
What exactly does that mean?
You're taking this
in a strange direction.
It may come into play later.
So... where should I start?
How 'bout from the beginning?
This could take a while.
Okay. Got it, Dutch.
So that's the deal. Yeah.
Well, that was good. It gave
me another piece of the puzzle.
How many pieces are left?
This better be all
the factions that are
based here in Roanapur or else!
Full house, you slut!
I just won me
three hundred bucks!
For fuck's sake!
The Lord loves those with
kind hearts and open wallets!
You always bet without thinking
when Rock's done something.
Come on. What did
he do this time
to piss you off so much,
Two Hands, huh?
Usually you're
joined at the hip.
It's dangerous! The problem
is who the maid's going after.
Oh? What did
these guys do wrong?
They blew the bitch's
master into a thousand pieces.
Explosive experts?
Courtesy of Uncle Sam
and some fuckin' GI Joes.
He was taken out
by the U.S. Army?
Yeah. The maid's gone berserk.
She's going to
grind those poor fucks up
and make hamburger out of them.
Hmm. Any idea why
those soldiers came to
this shithole
in the first place?
Beats me. I'm getting real tired
of helping him with this crap.
I'm tired of his crap.
I've gone through every possible
scenario. This just might work.
Yeah? Oh. It's you. What's up?
Fabiola, have you
heard from Mr. Rock?
That's the fourth time you've
asked me that this morning.
Oh. I guess you're right.
I should go make
a run through the city.
Maybe I'll find a
hint or a clue on my own.
Hey!
Sorry I took so long, guys!
What?
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Oh, no. To be honest, I didn't
think you were actually going to
come back and help us.
I approached it like a puzzle,
and once I did,
it got more interesting.
It's like I told you on the
phone. The maid came and left.
I don't know where she went.
Uh, say, what's
the story here?
My shop wasn't
the only place wrecked.
The whorehouse
upstairs is also toast
thanks to that
crazy little maid there.
I thought I'd chill
with the girls for a while.
You destroyed this man's bar?
I-I didn't mean to.
I said, "peacefully."
I know. Sorry.
Tell me, did you
help the maid, Bao?
Nope! Nuh, uh, uh! And
that's all you're gonna get,
cuz I don't
have to tell ya shit!
It's important, Bao.
Alright, but Rock...
Promise me.
If the shit hits the fan,
don't tell anyone
that I talked to you.
Of course.
I'm gonna have you
put that in writing.
This could get
me fuckin' killed.
So, about last night?
Right, last night.
Sorry, what'd you just say?
There's a war coming.
Who do I need to visit
in order to
acquire weapons? Please.
F-Forget it!
You're fucking
joking, right...?!
Bartender, do I
look like I'm joking?!
While I was making
some phone calls for her,
she was gobbling down
pills by the handful.
Almost like she was at a movie
munching on fuckin' popcorn.
And you told her
about Praiyachat, Torchy,
and the unlicensed
physician, Dr. Heartland.
Was the doctor so
she could get a refill?
Do I look fucking suicidal?
I didn't ask her shit.
Appreciate it, Bao.
I owe you for this.
Where's Two-Hands? It's
fucking weird to see you alone.
You lovebirds have a fight?
What? No.
Senor Rock!
Uh, yeah? What is it?
We just spent the whole day
walking around this cesspool
and the three people
who could have provided us
with a lead weren't home!
What exactly
is going on here?!
Uh, they have lives?
You promised we'd
find her! You promised!
This isn't a
surprise. Just relax.
Remember your head maid
is kinda notorious here.
People see a maid
wearing the same uniform
and a young aristocrat and of
course they're gonna disappear.
No one will talk to us
with you two tagging along
like a couple of puppy dogs.
Too bad, I'm not
ready to give up yet.
I'll come back tomorrow
and look by myself.
Fabiola, I'm sorry, but I
think this is too much for us.
But, why?
You're a brave one.
You don't seem intimidated
by this city at all.
The place I'm from
was full of lowlifes.
Just like this
festering pile of trash.
It's kind of like coming home.
Fabiola told me that she's
from the barrios of Caracas.
The barrios?
That's what they're called.
They're where the
homeless people live,
the slums of Caracas.
At night, that entire
area of the city
glitters like the Milky Way.
In case you're wondering
how it's possible for
people who have nothing
to light their shacks,
it's because everyone
steals their electricity
from the power company.
Really. They sound resourceful.
You're overestimating them.
But that's all in the past
because you're with us now!
Well, I come from a large
family of eleven, so I'm just
glad I could make things
a bit easier for my parents.
Is that where you
learned how to shoot
and do those fancy leg moves?
You dance?
Who me?
Shut up, you!
Fancy leg moves?
What does he mean?
Young Master.
He means capoeira.
You see... There was a
local from my neighborhood
who was studying at a dojo.
I learned it by playing
around and copying what he did.
I've heard of capoeira!
It's a martial art, right?
You have to teach
it to me, Fabiola!
I'm not an expert,
but sure, I could teach you.
Like I said, I didn't
live in a nice place
so I had to find
a way to stay safe.
Some way to protect myself.
You can accidentally
kill people with a gun,
but this way I could hold back.
That's why I thought capoeira
would be a great skill to learn.
You're absolutely right. I'm so
glad to hear you say that.
Look, I applaud you
guys for your beliefs...
But I'm not sure that's the
right attitude for this town.
I usually don't give
out advice, but here goes:
When you need
to pull the trigger,
don't think, don't hesitate.
And when you shoot,
make sure you shoot to kill.
That kind of
thinking is dangerous!
Look what it did to Roberta.
I don't want it to
happen to Fabiola, too.
Alright. Starting tonight
you'll be staying at
Mr. Chang's beach house.
A nice little hideout
with bodyguards and a pool.
We'll call it a day
after we drop you off.
Uh, yeah. We'll be in the car.
Come meet us when you're done.
That wasn't like you. You don't
usually give people advice.
Yeah, I know,
but I don't want those kids
to go out and
get themselves killed.
Don't worry,
I'm not gonna get
any more involved
with those two.
How much can your heart
take, when every death is
like another layer of
armor weighing you down?
That's why I don't
ask too many questions.
Rock, can you
carry that weight?
So, that's what this is about.
A silly turf war
between the CIA and the NSA.
If the Intelligence Community
had sanctioned the operation
they would have
definitely told me
and the other CIA
operatives in the area.
Depending on what they do next,
I'd like to use the
Church's network of informants.
This mess was started by Program
one-fourteen that called for
direct interference
in Venezuelan politics,
which they planned and carried
out without any input from us.
The CIA's primary
mission these days
is gathering
economic information.
Then we use it
to manipulate economies
in order to
expand our influence.
We think this
is far more efficient.
It's tough to be top dog.
You compete with yourselves.
Well, whatever.
We'll find out where
the NSA operatives are hiding.
It could take a while,
but something'll turn up.
Our specialty is
listening to the sinful.
Do your best, sister.
We'll see to it you
get paid for the information
and anything
else you come up with.
Uh, one other thing.
All of the mafias are holding a
summit meeting at the Golden
Swingy Night Club tonight.
It was organized by the Triad.
Garcia wasn't that impressed,
but the little maid was
pretty excited about staying
at Mr. Chang's beach house.
That's good.
Well, someone's distracted.
Those are the mob bosses. And
they're all headed the same way.
They're holding a meeting.
They have to
collaborate and swap intel.
Oh, makes sense.
It's all working
out just like I predicted.
So I guess
tonight's the night
they make a plan and
decide what to do with her.
Not yet. They're not
gonna do that right away.
They won't? But they
don't have much time.
They're in the same boat
as us and the Lovelace kid.
Dutch always says,
see how they divide
the spoils between themselves.
But, that'll be later.
I'm sure of it.
And then after
everything gets blown to hell,
they'll divide it up again.
Hey, Balalaika!
I got a bet that says
we're all here
celebrating your birthday.
You bring a cake?
I didn't know I was here
to listen to some
guido make me laugh.
I guess I can go now.
Fuck!
Easy there, Tomaso. This Russian
Doll was raised in Siberia,
she ain't civilized like us.
Oy, Amigos! Sorry
to ruin your good time,
but let's get down
to fucking business!
Yes, let's do that.
Right about now Chang will
be taking over the meeting.
He'll begin
talking about the maid
and telling
them who she's after.
But the guys who don't
understand how dangerous
the situation is
will interrupt him.
I got it! Easiest thing in the
fuckin' world to take care of!
We throw a party where the maid
and these goons can hash it out!
Get the champagne
flowing and have some
big titted dancers jump out
of one of them fuckin' cakes!
Were you this
funny when you were
telling jokes to
pig farmers in Sicily?
Fucking zip it,
you Ivan bitch!
Now, as I was saying...
The terrorists who
set off the bomb that
killed Diego Lovelace...
were professional soldiers.
Chang will tell them
who Roberta is tracking down,
and that will
get Balalaika's attention.
That's because the Russian mafia
she's in charge of is full of
ex-Soviet paratroopers. Soldiers
who were trained specifically
to engage with the U.S. military
should World
War Three break out.
But the Colombian
Cartel will have
a completely
different reaction.
This is a
perfect chance for us to
make good with
those FARC assholes.
I say we hunt
that fucking maid down
and serve her head
up on a silver platter.
Your bravery is
admirable, but misguided.
Our true enemy here are
the soldiers she's
hunting, not the maid.
It's obvious what the American's
goals are in all this.
To stop the drug trade!
We have to deal
with them without mercy
before their operation
affects our little town.
It's been thirty-five years
since this stinking wharf town
became a haven for
criminals from around the world.
The reason Roanapur is not
on the evening news or on the
minds of politicians is because
everyone here in this room,
everyone who rules
this city from the shadows,
all desire the same thing.
Our city is weak and fragile.
If we let people
from the outside step
into the ring with us
who do you think will be left
standing here
after the shooting stops?
My friends, no one will
be left. I won't, you won't.
The city itself won't be here.
Even if they realize
how much danger they're in,
they'll start looking.
But they're not going
to find Roberta right away.
Where is she?! I need more
clues. I need more information.
I just don't have enough
to work with! Damn it!
O Lord, I am weak.
I am a lowly sinner and
I beg your heavenly mercy,
my salvation can only be
through the glory of your grace.
Hear my prayer and
grant me the strength
to fight the sins that
you have revealed to me,
to do good in this world
as you have commanded me,
to overcome the obstacles
you place in my path, and to
You probably shouldn't
take any more of those pills.
They're already
affecting your mind.
I am a lowly sinner and
I beg your heavenly mercy,
After this, do you
plan on going back to that
lush garden with
all the beautiful orchids?
That boy will be
there waiting for you.
to overcome the obstacles
you place in my path,
and to endure the torments
that in your almighty wisdom
Be honest, is this
really about revenge?
Or do you think
it could be about you?
The Master and the
Young Master are good people
who deserve all the
blessings of Heaven above.
Please, O Lord! I alone
should suffer for my sins.
The sins are mine!
You can never
atone for your past sins.
Even if you live
a life of penance
and charity for
the rest of your days.
Even if you turn
your weapons on yourself.
You shut up!
Shut up. Shut up, shut up!
Hey!
Jesus H. Christ, wait a minute!
Don't shoot, it's me, Leroy!
I mean, what the fuck?!
Here, look, I got
the clothes you asked for!
Just put the gun down!
What about the recruiter?
Yeah. I talked
with the old guy.
Now it's just
a matter of the cash.
Wait a sec-- Weren't you--?
Who were you
talking to before?
Yeah, so? And what do
you want me to do about it?
We're running out of time here.
I have to find Roberta soon.
Rock, this is about
how you couldn't save that
Yakuza schoolgirl back in Japan,
isn't it? Is this penance?
No.
Sure it is. It's just
like when you tried to
save that little princess
and Sis handed you your ass.
It's starting
to get in your blood,
you're starting
to like the game.
Or maybe I just
fuckin' imagined that.
Hobby?
Yeah, that's right. I'm
really no different from you.
I'm sure that's what you said.
Some kind of fuckin' hobby.
What does that make
me if I tag along with you?
That's what I wanna know.
You've always been
there for me when my back
was against the wall.
I appreciate that.
He "appreciates" that.
You're something else.
If you want me to
join you at the gaming table,
I'm gonna need a
good song and dance
to keep
rolling those dice.
Why should I keep backing
you up when you double down?
Come on, I'm fuckin'
tired of wingin' it.
Remember when we were in Japan,
you said you were my gun.
If you're the gun,
then that means I'm the bullet.
But as a bullet I'm nothing
more than a chunk of lead.
If I hadn't come to this
city, I probably would have
spent the rest of
my life as a piece of lead.
But I did come.
All my life I've been waiting
for the gunpowder to go off.
You know what you need to ignite
gunpowder? You need a gun.
"Come on baby, light my fire."
What?
Don't you know it?
It's a classic by the Doors.
Rock, what type of ammo
are you? A full metal jacket?
A hollow-point? Or maybe
a Glaser Safety Slug?
Nah, you're like one
of those silver bullets,
nobody knows exactly
where it's gonna go.
You use it to
kill some freaky monster.
It's expensive
but it always works.
But you're fucked if
you use it at the wrong time.
Then the monster
eats your ass.
We're out of water.
There's a vending
machine downstairs.
Whoa.
Make yourself useful.
Hey, make sure you use bahts!
Don't use nickels or that
piece of shit'll break down!
No nickels, right!
Dammit. It's not fair.
Where you going? I was just
about to bring your water up.
Praiyachat should
be in right about now.
We have to get back
to the ship by sundown.
Let's hurry up and
get this over with, Rock.
Young Master!
Are you sleeping? Perfect!
Well, that looks relaxing!
You almost look happy!
We have a pool
back in Venezuela but
I'd never actually swum in one
before, so I thought why not?
I just wanted to
try it! Just for a while.
You don't have
to be so secretive,
you could've used it any time.
I apologize, Young Master!
Enough. Hey, "Young Master."
She can't tell you
she wants some time off
because you're being a little
prick about finding Four-Eyes.
Look... Mini-maid's not
going to come out and tell you
because she's so fucking loyal.
If you're gonna be the patriarch
of your screwed up family
you gotta figure that
bullshit out on your own.
I will not let you
use such language when
speaking to
the Young Master!
That was good
advice, ya bitch!
We'll try all the same
people we went to yesterday.
I swear I'm going to skin
you alive, you little twat!
Is the old fart in? It's
Rebecca from the Lagoon Company.
Step on in, Revy! How your
Cutlasses holding up, huh?
The boys are still awesome!
But I didn't come here today
for that. It's something else.
Another maid? So, you want
me to outfit this one, too?
Sounds like proof
that she did come here.
She looked like
this one only taller
and wearing glasses, right?
It was Bao who introduce her.
I let her in even
though I never see her before.
What did she
come here for? Weapons?
No, she got gun.
She want me to work
on gun that she bring herself.
Museum piece,
old Flintlock rifle.
It made in Spain,
eighteenth century.
Young Master!
There's no mistake.
It's the gun we had
on display in the main hall!
She want me to restore
it so she could shoot it.
It's condition was "meh."
It not much trouble.
She also looking for black
powder, but I don't have that.
So that's why
she went to Torchy!
Yeah.
Hey, Revy! Grip
on this one all bang up!
The fuck-- What else am I
gonna use to crack skulls open?
FAY-FAY duh PEE-yen,
this piece is top of line!
Torchy! You still
sell gunpowder?
Keep that bitch away from me!
She's got mind control powers,
the aluminum
foil isn't working!
She's come here to
suck my brains outta my skull!
Bring it!
You fuckin' alien bitch!
Uh, I'm an alien?!
This loser's strung
out, just play along.
"That's right,
she's an alien!
She's got a spaceship
parked right out back...
But she's one
of the good aliens!"
I don't trust her!
I see you're as punctual
as ever, Mr. Chang.
It's one of my virtues.
Now let's get to it.
You're sure?
A woman didn't pick it up?
It's kinda hazy.
It was a private dick
or a snitch or something.
What was that
moron's name again?
Leave your
fuckin' smack alone
when you're talkin'
to someone, ya tweaker!
Who's the delivery boy?
Shit! I can't focus. I bet I
could remember if I just fixed.
You don't mind, right, Revy?
Like hell!
The infiltration team
is a special NSA unit that
carries out
sensitive orders direct from
the highest
levels of government.
They're called Task
Force Nine and they belong to
the Pentagon's
special ops command, SOCOM.
In the military
organization table,
they're the Fifty-sixth
Construction Battalion.
But the Joint Chiefs of Staff
have given them another name.
They call the team
"Gray Fox Command Group."
I guess that's fitting.
The bloodhound is
chasing down the foxes.
Their primary mission is to
infiltrate the Golden Triangle
and capture Khun Sa's right
hand man, General Shi Yan.
The General is to
be extradited in order to
face charges before
the U.S. Supreme Court.
I believe that
would be a most unfortunate
turn of events for the Triad.
Without the
General's poppy fields,
the Triad's heroin refinement
plant would have to shut down.
When will this take place?
The end of this month.
There are eighteen men in
the assault force stationed
in the red-light district.
While they wait
for deployment orders,
they're posing as backpackers
at the following staging points:
Fire Team Alpha
is at Hotel Tokaina.
Fire Team Bravo
is at the Blue Moon.
Fire Team Charlie
is at Ramsap Inn.
Commanding Officer
Major Shane Charlie Caxton
is with Fire Team Alpha.
You've given me
more than enough, Mr. CIA.
I'm not done yet.
Tell me how
you're going to respond.
What, you think this
makes us friends or something?
You're some bureaucrat posted
to a miserable backwater,
and you think you're going
to use us to do your dirty work?
You couldn't be more wrong!
Let me warn you right now.
We are more than mere
government bureaucrats.
Think of the United
States as a giant hydra
with countless heads
snaking all over the world.
You may have the
power to make individuals
and companies
submit to your will.
But we have the means
to destroy entire countries.
We have no equals in the world.
We are the highest
authority there is.
And that's why
it'd be a mistake to
underestimate my organization,
you two-bit thug.
Uh, what was it, Luh,
la, Larry, Laurie, Leroy, uh-
Wait that's it!
It's Richie Leroy!
Richie Leroy is
working for the maid!
He's the final piece
of the puzzle! Hang on!
The Young Master
is waiting at the manor
for me to bring back
the heads of the foxes.
He will smile at me
and then everything will
return to the way it used to be.