[alarm]
[ROCK] Over the past year,
I've woken up with hangovers
in a lot of places.
Let's see... Sometimes it's
the cabin of the torpedo boat.
Sometimes the office
of a delivery company.
But usually,
this is the place.
A cheap hotel room overlooking
downtown Roanapur.
For the first time in a year,
I'm leaving this
city to go far away.
To a place that
I used to call home.
That's where I'm headed.
[BENNY] Oh, that you, Rock?
Happy New Year!
Although, it's pretty hard
to get in the mood here
when no one's celebrating.
Uh-huh, just a couple
of firecrackers.
[ROCK] Yeah? Well, they've got
everything nicely decorated
for the New Year here.
[BENNY] And how's Revy doing?
[ROCK] So far,
all she does is complain.
She didn't like the
Tokarev she was given.
She was in a bad mood all
day yesterday 'cause of that.
[BENNY] You're quite
the ladies man,
You know she only went 'cause
she was worried about you.
[ROCK] Yeah.
I'd better get going.
I'll talk to you soon.
[REVY] Look. It started snowing.
They definitely get a lot less
snow here than in New York.
But just seeing it
again reminds me.
Last time I saw snow,
I was still living there.
That was ages ago.
So, whaddya think?
I've been hit on by
a few guys already.
When I say something, they
look at me like I'm retarded
and say " Gaijin, gaijin. "
This country pisses me off.
[BANDO speaking in Japanese]
How should he address you?
Just Balalaika is fine.
I've been briefed by Laptev.
We've been eager to set up
base of operations in
Tokyo for quite some time.
So, your assistance
is greatly appreciated.
[BANDO speaking in Japanese]
But isn't the Washimine Family
part of the council?
[ROCK translating]
We can only go so far
in meeting the
council's call to duty.
We've gone to great lengths
to fulfill our
obligation to them.
But they continue
to disrespect us
by keeping us at the
bottom of the family ranks.
It would appear
that our interests
are mutually
beneficial, Mr. Bando.
You wish to expand your
influence with our help.
And of course, we wish
to establish ourselves
in this city.
[speaking in Japanese]
[BALALAIKA] That's funny.
You're concerned
about our forces?
Let me assure you,
our forces are nothing
like those in this country.
In essence, we're a
military force, Mr. Bando.
Let me show you.
[cellphone ringing]
It's me. Case eight ready?
Very well.
[speaking in Japanese]
Unit 5-5. Finish the job.
[explosion]
[screams from crowd]
[ROCK speaking in Japanese]
[speaking in Japanese]
[BALALAIKA] Intimidation with
handguns will amount to nothing.
We've opted to make
our strength known
with the first strike.
This is what we
of Hotel Moscow
consider a true
show of force.
We will not hesitate to destroy
that which stands in our way,
do you understand?
That means decimating
anything and anyone.
[speaking in Japanese]
[REVY] Those yakuza
were scared shitless.
I don't think they make
women like Balalaika in Japan.
This isn't quite the
homecoming I'd expected.
I'd rather they didn't turn
my country into a war zone.
Old Fry Face was in
a pretty good mood.
There hasn't been a
big fight in Roanapur
for a while now, so she's
probably itching for it.
I'm telling you, she
gets off on this shit.
She'd give up sex before
she passed up a war.
[ROCK] Something's
wrong with her.
All of them are war maniacs.
I'm guessing they left
a few important screws
back in Afghanistan.
Uh... Hey, Rock.
What is that?
Oh. It's a neighborhood fair.
It's almost the New Year.
So, it's like a carnival.
Sounds like a good
time. Yo, driver!
[DRIVER] Alright. Here you go.
Hey, Rock, where the fuck
are all the rides?
[ROCK] You won't find any at
a traditional Japanese fair.
[REVY grumbling]
Here you go.
[REVY] Yeah,
that's my third one!
Well, I suppose they don't
call you Two-Hands
for nothing, right?
Got that right.
As if you ever had any doubts.
I'm Miss Rebecca.
Give me a gun and I'll
show you why they call me
the best shot in the East.
Number four.
It's too bad I don't
have my Cutlass.
I could close this shop
down in three seconds.
Of course, it's next
to fuckin' impossible
to have a gunfight
in this country.
And you can't bribe the cops
like you can in Roanapur.
If we get thrown in jail...
You remembering something?
Huh? Like what?
[REVY] What do you mean,
"Like what?"
This is where
you're from, isn't it?
Don't you have anyone here?
You know. Like
family or someone.
It's not like you were born from
the crotch of a tree, right?
[ROCK] I thought nosy types
weren't too popular.
[REVY] It's nothing.
Just wondering what you
were thinking, that's all.
You looked like you were lost
in thought for a second there.
[ROCK] I still remember the day
you first pulled a gun on me.
One year ago. Time flies.
[REVY] Yeah.
I don't understand it.
I used to know this
place so well, but
now I feel like I don't
know it at all anymore.
My... family doesn't
exactly get along.
My older brother turned out well
and got a government job.
But I got into college a year
late and that was that.
They didn't expect much.
In the end, I guess
they didn't really care.
[REVY] But your folks
are alive, right?
You should at least
get in touch with them.
I mean, c'mon, you
haven't been arrested yet.
Could be your last chance.
In our line of work,
it's only a matter of time.
From my point of view,
your family is normal.
Isn't it worth it to
at least go visit them?
I mean, you've
managed to get this far
without stealing or
killing anyone, right?
Look, don't get me wrong.
I'm just saying you
might regret it...
...if you don't
go and see 'em.
I can't say that
I'm really normal.
The fact that I'm hanging
around with you guys
should be proof of that.
[chuckles]
What is it?
[REVY] Alright! One more shot
and I get the grand prize!
What the fuck?!
This thing must
be weighted down!
[ROCK] What're you doing?!
Yeah!
Tell him, Rock!
Huh?
Excuse me, my friend there
just got your top score,
and she'd like to
collect her prize now.
No way. She doesn't get
a prize for cheating.
He says it doesn't count
because you used your
gun to knock it down.
Fucking asshole!
Hey, that's bullshit!
You won't get away with
this, you cocksucker!
Get out of my face,
you arrogant Yankee bitch!
What was that?!
Maybe I should use real
bullets instead, huh?!
[ROCK] C'mon, Revy!
Just let it go!
[REVY] Shut up!
I gotta teach this cocksucker
a fuckin' lesson!
[MAN] Typical American!
Come to my country
and tell me what to do?!
--Ginji.
--[REVY] Rotten son of a bitch!
Excuse me.
May I have a word?
[REVY] Huh?!
We're in the middle of
New Year's celebrations.
Why don't we all
just try to have fun?
Please, miss.
I urge you to lay
your aggression aside.
And who the fuck are you?!
Revy, let's go!
We're being a nuisance.
It sounds like you're
taking his side, Rock.
[GINJI] If you're going
to be unreasonable,
we have a problem.
However, the way
I see it, life is short,
so why don't we all
just try to enjoy
what little time we're given?
Listen to me.
You've had your fun,
so please take advantage of
this opportunity to save face.
Hmph! Fuck that!
[ROCK] Revy! Just let it go!
It's not worth it!
[YUKIO] Um...
Sweet sake...
Huh?
I, um... Sweet sake, anyone?
It's just so cold tonight,
I thought rather
than standing out...
Who the fuck are you?
But, miss...
[ROCK] Yes, I agree
with the young lady.
I'm not a big
fan of fighting,
so sake it is. Alright?
[REVY] Um, how the fuck
did we end up like this?
[ROCK] It's not so bad.
Besides, there's nothing to
gain from making a big scene.
Shit, I'm not even
in the mood anymore.
The buzz is gone.
Well, thank god for that.
I'm really glad that
you accepted my offer
before things escalated.
--Ah, well,
--I, uh...
Oh, you were
saying something?
Sorry. Go ahead. I didn't
mean to cut you off.
I was just...
I was just... gonna say
you look like a student.
Or maybe you're
one of the vendors?
Oh?
Well, yes. Actually, I'm both.
You see, my father was, um...
My father was
actually a vendor.
And that man, Mr. Ginji,
well, my father was
pretty much his mentor.
If there's ever any kind
of a dispute around here,
everyone goes to Ginji.
He's big, huh?
Anyway, before
he realized it,
Ginji had become the
arbitrator of Takamachi.
Is that so?
I came here after
my cram school tonight
to help Ginji close up shop.
So, this was quite a shock.
I bet. I'm afraid she can
be pretty short-tempered.
I'm just glad everything
turned out okay.
I'm curious...
Your friend,
is she... Japanese?
No, she's from the States.
She's Chinese-American.
How should I put it...
Uh... we work for
the same company.
I'm here to translate
for a Russian.
She came with me.
Wow, an international
career! Impressive.
I dunno about that.
The company's small
and it can be quite stressful.
It's hard work
and often dangerous.
Your job is dangerous?
Ah, well, um...
Yeah, something like that.
Tch! If they keep this up,
I'm gonna puke.
[chuckles]
What are you
laughing at, asshole?
[GINJI] Miss.
You're not a decent
woman, are you?
There. It's those eyes.
Those aren't the
eyes of a human being.
Those are the
eyes of a rabid dog.
[REVY] Ha! Well, there's one
I've never heard before,
but all the same,
I get your point.
You and I are the same type.
You stink of blood and guts.
No mistaking it.
Damn, it's starting
to get cold.
Well, Miss, I think
it's time I got you home.
Okay.
Goodbye.
[ROCK] And that was how we met.
Oh, by the way,
what's your name?
[YUKIO] Right. It's Yukio.
It was a pleasure talking
to you. Take care!
[ROCK] That day...
...I still didn't know
just how powerful
the pull of the
underworld can be.
But I'd learn.
[BORIS] 0230 hours.
We've assaulted
a Kousa Clan office.
Confirmed outcome.
Twelve kills, no fatalities,
no casualties.
All men left the
scene by 0237 hours.
Shall I have them prepare some
Russian tea instead, Ma'am?
[BALALAIKA] No, I don't
like to make a fuss.
Some toast, perhaps?
Would you like
toast, Sergeant?
No, I don't have
any appetite.
You know you shouldn't
skip breakfast, Sergeant.
It's not healthy.
And when did
the police arrive?
[BORIS] They closed off the
scene at exactly 0305 hours.
They're now on a heightened
security status.
I had the Washimine
Clan transcribe
their wireless
communications.
We'll have to wait
for Rock's translation
before we can
confirm any details.
The reliability
of this information
could very well mean
life or death for us.
Right.
[LAPTEV] Heh. You don't
disappoint, Balalaika.
I'm starting to understand
why Boss Slevenin
speaks so highly of you.
Is that so?
And whose ass do you think
I'm here to wipe, Vasily?
You've single-handedly
destroyed our reputation here.
This place is a playground,
but you still
couldn't take control.
I want to wrap up this operation
and get back to Roanapur.
That place is a
real powder keg.
I can't leave it
unattended for long.
I'll be seeing
you in six hours.
[LAPTEV] You forget yourself!
Back in Moscow, I'm one of
the highest-ranked bosses,
so show a little respect!
I'm sorry.
It's hard for me to
remember the bosses
who rose up using
money instead of skill.
I'd better write your
name on a dollar bill
so I don't forget
who you are.
[LAPTEV] Apologize!
You lousy ex-military bitch!
[BALALAIKA] Let me explain
something to you.
There are two things in this
world that I just cannot stand.
One is cold blintzes
and the other is useless,
incompetent,
ex-KGB shitheads.
Now I suggest you
keep your head low
so the bullets don't hit you.
Hey, Boss.
[BANDO] You know what, Ginji?
The new generation would
rather plug into video games
than play with these.
How much longer are you
planning to endure this life?
[GINJI] For better or for worse,
this is the job of a vendor.
With all due respect, Boss,
it's a lot better than selling
meth and women for a living.
[BANDO] Are you implying that
I do this because I like it?
You think I wanted this?
When the old man died,
he left us with a family
that can barely get tribute.
Truth is the only reason this
clan still exists in this city,
is because the old man and
the Kousa Clan's last head
were sworn brothers.
Now that they're gone,
what have we got?
It's been almost
three years now
and they still won't
let us name a successor.
We're the only ones left who're
still loyal to the old man.
He took me in
and got me set up
when I came over
here from Kansai.
That's why I'm here. It falls
to us to do something.
Ginji. You said that
dealing with low-lifes
brought shame upon the yakuza.
However, that only
matters if we have a name.
That's not what the
old man would've said.
I'm pulling off
a big job right now.
I've enlisted the
help of the Russians
to take care of the council.
[GINJI] Do you realize
what you're saying?
They tried to take us
out first, didn't they?!
All the same,
Russians are Russians
no matter who they are.
It goes without saying, they
don't have a shred of honor.
Which is why we need
to maintain control
of certain key areas.
[GINJI] So, what are
you trying to say?
[BANDO] Ginji, I need you
to take it up again.
That famous
white scabbard.
Only one name
still strikes fear
into the hearts of all yakuza.
"Man-slayer Ginji."
I beg you, take up the
sword this one last time.
Look, Boss...
I'm indebted to you
for looking after the
young lady as you have.
I'll never forget that.
I also understand what
you're saying. But...
You cannot look
me in the eye
and tell me there
is any honor in this.
Back when I took up the white
scabbard for the old man,
it was because he had honor.
[BANDO] I guess that's that.
I'll see you later.
[GINJI] Those Russians...
Hmm?
[GINJI] Did they bring
their own interpreter?
Yeah, but why do you ask?
What did you make of him?
I dunno. Well-mannered
young kid.
Had a girl with him
who looked like trouble.
He looked just like
an average guy.
There was something
about him, though.
If I had to
make an analogy,
he's kinda like the chicken
that shows up at your doorstep,
carrying soup stock, onions,
and even the pot
to cook himself in.
Uh, this shouldn't
take too long, okay.
--[REVY] Mhm.
--[ROCK] See ya.
Shoo. Hurry up and go.
Shoo, shoo.
I'll be waiting
here for you,
but not forever.
Just until I finish
drinking this.
After that, I'm leaving...
partner.
[dog barking]
--I got you!
--Got you first!
No, you're dead!
Whaddya know.
The sky looks the same
no matter where you are.
Whether it's here
or back on Mott Street.
Hey! You goddamn brats!
You wanna shoot each
other in the streets,
then why don't you
head on over to Lebanon!
What do we have here?
You're a real gunman, are you?
But just look at this
sorry excuse for a gun.
Okay, you brats!
Keep your eyes on those cans
we got lined up there, alright?
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Holy cow!
--[BOY 1] She got 'em all!
--[BOY 2] That was sweet!
That's right.
Just like Annie Oakley.
Jack McCall! I'm here
to avenge Wild Bill!
Can you outdraw
Calamity Jane?
Go on. Take your best shot.
Ah! Ya got me!
[BOY 3] I've been hit!
Whoa, whoa.
What was that?!
Sorry, but you've got
this dying thing all wrong.
Only place you'll see people
go down like that is in movies.
In reality, you just suddenly
lose all your strength.
Do ya understand?
It's like everything below
your knees disappears,
then you lose balance
and go down head-first.
I'll show you what I mean.
You there.
Ahhh!
Lady, if that's what it's
like to die, it kinda sucks.
I'm sorry, but that's
just how it is when you die.
In real life, dying
never looks that coo--
What are you doing?
How long have
you been watching?
Since about the time you charged
into the Deadwood Saloon.
That's a different ending
from what I remember.
Calamity Jane didn't die
at that exact location.
Goddamn it, Rock.
Hey, that's my gun!
[REVY] Listen up! If you tell
Dutch or Benny about this,
I swear to God,
I'll cut your balls off
and feed them to you on
the end of a fuckin' skewer!
[ROCK] Okay!
I won't say a thing!
So, were you able to
meet up with your folks?
Oh. W-Well, I did end
up going to the house,
but... I didn't see them.
There was no one there.
[REVY chuckles]
What is it?
[REVY] Nah, it's nothing.
Anyway, we're still here
for a few more days.
[ROCK] Hm. You're right.
[REVY] I don't get it.
Why won't he just go home?
It's like this place is made
for him. He belongs here.
[kids laughing]
[YOSHIDA] Boss! The Russians are
going completely crazy on us!
They've gone and blown
something else up today!