What's with that
look, huh, sweetheart?
After all that, you still wanna
act like nothing's wrong.
Go ahead. Keep
looking down at us.
But after we get
rid of sword-boy,
and if we can't find
a buyer for you...
...I'm gonna pimp your
ass to a client of mine.
He's a crackhead and
a real fucking sicko.
This guy can't
even get a hard-on
unless it's hardcore S&amp;M.
You'll both get high,
then he's gonna beat off
while you eat his shit.
Let's see how fucking
proud you are then.
Oh yeah. But don't worry.
When the video comes out,
I'll be sure to buy a copy.
[THUG 1] You're full of shit.
You can't win that much
playing Mahjong. Dumbass.
[THUG 2] Oh yeah?
You wanna piece of this?
[THUG 1] Aw, shit,
my Zippo's outta fuel.
--You got any?
--[THUG 3] Oh yeah,
did you hear about the guy who
pulled that job at Shin-Okubo?
[THUG 2] Yeah, this guy
went after some Iranian dude
with a knife or somethin'?
[THUG 1] Well,
there's a warrant out
for the guy's arrest and...
--Eh?
--[THUG 1] Huh?
Ahh!
Huh? What the fuck?
Keep it down, would ya?!
[YUKIO gasps]
Hey, look at that.
He actually came.
Sword-boy to the rescue.
And you brought
Revy with you.
I wasn't expecting you, baby.
I guess you did
wanna fuck, huh? Cool!
[YUKIO] Gin...
Ginji!
You've gone too far...
You damn fools!
Did you want to see
my sword that badly?!
Heh, heh!
[GINJI] So be it.
You can all make the
march to Hell... together!
Kill 'em all, baby!
Ahh!
[CHAKA] Holy shit!
Would you look at this!
I've never seen a fight
this good in my life!
Hey, you pussies!
Don't fucking hide!
Show some balls, goddamn it!
Let's go! Move it! Run!
[REVY] Your turn, Jumbo.
Wow! Pretty impressive!
Guess it's time for
me to get serious.
Hey, Yukio! Come here!
Miss!
Over here!
You're gonna have
to come and get her!
Goddamn! That woman
is fucking amazing!
I never thought
I'd get the chance
to go one-on-one with her!
I'd better prepare the stage
if we're gonna do this right!
Know wha--ahhh!
--Huh?
--[CHAKA] Motherfucker!
Who the hell spilled
this shit?!
Cleaning fluid?
[ROCK] Hey!
Huh?
Fuck you!
Wait! Don't
fucking shoot me!
I give... I give up!
Yeah. Huh... huh.
Give! Give! I-I...!
"Give"? Give me what?
Please, no! I-I wanna
give you... I wanna--
You said you were gonna
"give" me something, right?
Well, spit it out!
I'm right here,
what the fuck are
you gonna give me?
But I give up! Seriously!
I give, I give, I give...
[REVY] Would you quit
your fuckin' babbling?
You gonna give
it to me or not?
C'mon!
Hey, Jumbo!
The game's up.
Boy, did we make a mess.
All we've got left to
do is mop this place up.
We should split up and
look for our princess
and that other piece of shit.
We'll go around the hallway
and meet at the pool, okay?
And by the way,
if you see Rock,
bring him with you, alright?
If we're lucky, he might
already be with the princess.
Well, I'll be counting
on you, partner.
Man. This guy's a stiff.
Now let's see...
I really pity you guys.
This is the end of the line.
The only way you're getting
outta here is in a body bag.
You understand
what I'm saying?
You're spending the
night in Hell's Motel.
And not one of you is
gonna check out alive.
Better start running
'cause the boogeyman's
coming to eat you up!
Too easy.
No one lives forever... baby.
[THUG 4] Hold on,
I don't hear nothin'.
Hey, Boss. Do you think the
rest of the guys are still...?
Um, Mr. Chaka!
[CHAKA] Shut up! I heard you
the first time, dip-shit!
Look, if I had to guess,
I'd say they're
all dead by now.
Huh?
What the hell is that?!
Those are your
men, you bastard!
Look at me, motherfucker!
I'm sick of following you!
[gunshot]
[THUG 5] Oh, fuck...
[CHAKA] Instead of wasting
your time bitching at me,
why don't you go
look for the girl?
Well, whaddya gonna do?
Only the strong survive, right?
Come on now!
Huh? You're running?
Fine then!
Damn it!
[REVY] Well, well, well...
Why am I not surprised?
Shooting your own
subordinates in the back.
You can't stoop much lower
than that, now can you?
Seeing as your arms and
legs aren't missing yet,
I guess you haven't
met up with Jumbo.
[CHAKA] Hmp. He can kiss my ass.
You're the one I've been
waiting to meet, Revy.
Truth is I've never met
a lady gunman before.
And now here
we are together.
I wanna fuck you... Revy.
[REVY] I make it a point
never to fuck assholes...
...or pussies.
When this can hits the floor,
that'll be our
signal, kitty-cat.
Ready?
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
What the...?
You wanted to challenge
me to a gunfight?
Don't make me laugh!
[CHAKA groaning]
You think I'd
waste the energy
drawing on a third-rate
sack of shit like you?
Dumb fuck.
Don't get me wrong,
I'd love to kill you.
But if you're actually happy to
die, that's a different story.
You've wasted
enough of my time.
I'm gonna let
Jumbo finish you off.
[CHAKA] How dare you,
you fucking bitch!
Get back here!
Sack o' shit.
[CHAKA] Don't you walk away!
Stop, goddamn it!
You hear me?!
[REVY] Sorry to keep you
waiting there, Jumbo.
Anyway, I brought
you your prom date.
[CHAKA] To hell with this shit.
You know, you're really starting
to get on my nerves, sword-boy.
Anyway, you're
wasting your time.
'Cause I already shot her.
[chuckling]
[GINJI] That's hard
for me to believe,
'cause I don't think
there's any way
that a treacherous
little dog like you
would ever destroy
his own paycheck.
Isn't that right?
A-Alright then, you bastard!
Looks like we're done talking!
'Bout time... I've been
waiting to see this.
Draw whenever you're ready.
Hmph!
Ahh!
Uh! Ahh!
[splash]
You bastards!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'll kill you!
[ROCK] It's gotten
awfully quiet.
That probably
means Revy and Ginji
are almost
finished up there.
But we should stay here
a bit longer just in case.
[YUKIO] Mr. Okajima...
--Hmm?
--[YUKIO] Why are you here?
[ROCK] I couldn't
just leave you alone.
Not after I found out...
that you were being dragged
into this situation
against your will.
[YUKIO] Right.
So, you don't know yet.
Hmm?
I get it.
You just said that I was being
dragged into this, right?
You're mistaken, Mr. Okajima.
The truth is...
...I am the person at
the center of all this.
And you... you are
now my enemy.
[gasp]
I'll say it again--
you're my enemy.
[ROCK] Yukio!
What are you saying?!
Mr. Okajima,
listen to me.
I am now the fourteenth
head of the Washimine Family.
In other words,
for all purposes,
I now hold the highest rank
within the Washimine Family.
So, you see... I was not
dragged into this situation.
I'm at the very center of it.
And as I said...
you're my enemy now.
[ROCK] But you...!
Damn it! You knew what
you'd be getting into,
and yet you still
stepped forward?!
You've seen it! None of these
guys have a shred of honor!
They're evil! This is a world
where people will betray
and kill one another as if it
doesn't mean anything at all!
[YUKIO] Mr. Okajima.
I'll ask you again.
Why are you here?
What possible reason
could you have?
[ROCK] I already told you why.
I couldn't just sit back
and watch you get
dragged into this.
[YUKIO] Couldn't watch, huh?
It's my understanding
that Mr. Bando committed
suicide. Is it true?
[gasps]
Tell me you weren't
watching when it happened.
With the family
going nowhere,
neglected by the council,
we either had to fight
or face being
swallowed up entirely.
Now what if you're
the only person
who can stop this
from happening?
In that position, would
you do any different?
For the brotherhood
to be renewed,
the successor has to
be a blood relative.
That was the condition.
[ROCK] But--
You don't have to
say it. I know.
It's an outdated custom that
no one's bothered to change.
But as foolish as
it may sound to you,
those are the rules
we must live by,
whether we like it or not.
That's how order
is maintained.
[ROCK] But that's crazy!
Say what you want, but then
what happens to your life?!
Nobody wanted this
for you! No one!
Not Bando, Ginji,
and certainly not you!
From what you told me,
everyone in your
life was desperate
to keep you away from
the fighting, right?
To keep you from standing
where you are now!
[YUKIO] Perhaps...
But if I'd been
standing here sooner,
maybe this wouldn't
have happened.
Bullshit! You had nothing
to do with what happened!
I guess... somehow you
must feel responsible
for what's happening
to your family.
That's the only way
I can make sense of this.
[YUKIO] Do you remember what we
talked about... at the café?
You know... how
people are like dice.
I've heard it said
that people are like dice.
"Like dice, we can throw
ourselves in any direction.
And that's why we're
condemned to be free."
So, you see, I wasn't
forced into this.
I chose to do it.
I chose to do my
part for my father
and those who loved him.
No! That's not true!
You were never given a choice!
If you lose sight of
that, you'll be forced
to carry this burden
that should never
have been yours
in the first place!
Right now,
you're in the twilight.
Wha...?
[YUKIO] You can say those things
because you've always
remained in the twilight!
You've never had to choose!
You say I had no choice!
If I don't believe
that I chose this,
I can't have resolve!
If someone's life,
their honor,
and their entire
future depends on me,
then of course I'm
going to fight for them!
What kind of person
wouldn't do that?!
Look at tonight!
If I didn't think
I'd chosen this,
I couldn't have endured it!
[sobbing]
[ROCK] Revy...
[REVY] Yeah, I believed
in God right up until
that night the cops
beat the hell outta me
for no reason at all.
I'll say this once--
next time you decide you're
gonna tell me what's proper,
you'll no longer be one of us.
[ROCK] All this time...
and nothing's changed.
Revy...
In the midst of
this cruel night
that this girl
has just endured,
I feel powerless to help.
I realize that my words will
never bring comfort to her,
as she's stumbling
toward your world.
I...
I'm right here where
I'm sitting, Revy.
I'm not anywhere else.
That's a lie.
Let's face it... I'm
not sitting anywhere!
You bastard!
You're evil!
You're the devil!
You deserve a much
more painful death,
but I suppose
this will suffice.
I decided that it
would be worth it.
I would carry
this great weight
on my shoulders,
and mine alone.
As long as it
meant that I could
save Ginji and the others,
then I knew I could bear it.
Y-Yukio, do you
really believe--
Mr. Okajima.
Answer me now!
What reason did you have for
making a stand here tonight?
To be completely
honest with you,
I couldn't really relate
to what you were saying
in the café that time...
But I think I'm starting
to understand you now.
It's funny. The reason
you submerged yourself
in the southeast Asian
underworld is probably because
you were looking for
something different...
...from Japan
and your daily life.
Nothing's really
changed for you
because you still
haven't decided.
You dread returning to your
normal life under the sun,
but you're afraid to go any
further into the darkness.
You're undecided,
hesitating between two lives.
No, I...
You said it earlier...
that you wanted to save me.
Well, then save me!
Save our family!
Save Ginji, the members,
and everyone else, too!
But that'll never
happen, will it?
Because the truth is you don't
actually want to save me.
I remind you of the normal life
you thought you'd thrown away.
That's all this is.
If you sit back
and watch me die,
you'd be losing the very
last of your recollections
of this normal life in Japan.
You don't want to
lose anything, do you?
Not even the life you threw
away. You still yearn for it,
but you don't want
it enough to keep it.
If that's the way you are,
how will you ever
choose to save someone?!
If you can't even
change your own life,
how can you change
someone else's?!
So, tell me! Go on! Tell me!
You know...
I wanted a normal life.
If life was fair, I'd be in
your shoes instead of mine.
I wouldn't have to
live a life of pain.
Yukio...
[YUKIO] Stay away from me.
Look, I know...
I'm just upset.
Still, I can't help
but envy your freedom.
And that's why...
I hate you so much.
Wait a sec.
I gotta say, that thing
you did was pretty amazing.
The bullet, baby.
You cut the bullet.
You sure you don't wanna show
me that trick one more time?
C'mon. Please?
That would be a big mistake.
I still owe you and
the interpreter a favor.
There's no point
in squandering that.
If you're lucky...
No... unlucky, we'll have
other opportunities to fight.
Yukio.
I thank you for your help.
I'll never forget
what you did. However...
...I pray that we never
meet again, Mr. Okajima.
Hmm...
[BORIS] Looks like Rock still
hasn't returned to his room.
What the hell is he
wasting his time on?
[BALALAIKA] It's just as well.
We've got nothing for
him to do at the moment.
The assault on
the Washimine Clan
will commence at
0750 as planned.
I want two squads to go in
and destroy their
headquarters first.
We'll also hit their offices
and confirmed safe houses.
[BORIS] Operation is a go.
The attack squad
is out and en route.
[BALALAIKA] What I want here
is a thorough elimination
of all Washimine forces.
Let's make this count.
The time has now come for
us to teach these Japanese
the art of war.
[BALALAIKA] I don't
know what's going on
in that head of yours,
but it will only bring
you disappointment
if you hope to have
a life like his.