[dogs growling]
[dogs snarling]
Are you ready, sora mea ?
[GRETEL] Yes. We won't be
coming back here again.
So, whatever we need,
we should take with us, okay?
[HANSEL] I know that, sora mea .
Here, fratele meu .
You be sora mea .
[HANSEL] Yes, fratele meu .
Shall we go now, sora mea ?
[GRETEL] Don't forget
our tickets and passports.
[HANSEL] I'd never do that.
Without those,
we can't go anywhere.
They won't let us
through any borders.
Let us be on our way,
fratele meu .
Indeed.
[giggling]
[dogs growling]
[barking]
[gunshots and dogs yelping]
[ROCK] Yes. Yes,
that's exactly it.
That was what
reminded me. Right.
[BALALAIKA] Hmm...
Thank you, Rock. I'll be
sure to return the favor.
Well, Rock recognized
the language.
Apparently, these kids are
from Count Dracula's homeland.
[BORIS] They're Romanian.
Ah, of course they are!
There were Romanian
troops in Kabul.
Damn, I thought those
phrases sounded familiar.
I should've known.
[BALALAIKA] As people get older,
remembering things becomes
quite the task, Sergeant.
It's the same with me.
Rowan, the owner of the
porn shop on Rachiada Street
secretly distributes black
market videos, doesn't he?
[BORIS] Yes, I believe so.
But what about him?
[gasping]
Oh, god...
[thunder]
[gun cocking]
[BALALAIKA] I take it you've
already swept this area clean?
[CHANG] This is all
very secretive.
If you wanted to go on a date,
you should've just asked me.
Well, you can't exactly
go for dinner and a movie
when you've got the
smell of blood on you.
Chang, we know
who's behind this now.
[CHANG] I see.
That's an intriguing subject.
How did you end up finding out?
As a matter of fact...
...we found what we were
looking for in Rowan's shop.
Pink shop Rowan?
So, I take it you invited
him to your office.
The poor bastard must've
been scared to death.
Let's just say the
back seat of that Benz
will never be the same.
That is unfortunate.
My specific request was for
Eastern European kiddy porn
featuring Romanian twins.
And snuff films, as well.
An hour later, he had
250 titles for me.
Huh. Again, unfortunate.
[BALALAIKA] I spent a night
and half of the next day
looking through
these videos made
for pedophiles and perverts,
until I eventually
hit the jackpot.
[crying]
Hansel and Gretel.
That's what the little brats
were called in the video.
After Ceausescu was overthrown,
many children were
sold to the black market
by institutions that
could no longer afford them.
Illegitimate children
of a fallen dictator.
[CHANG] Turned into toys
for child molesters,
they usually end up
as pig food.
I'm guessing that's what
these brats were destined for.
So, how did they escape it?
[BALALAIKA] Hmph!
For added entertainment,
the perverts filming this stuff
made these kids take
part in the killings.
They were required
to kill other children--
kids who were more or less
in the same situation as them.
In order to stay alive,
these kids desperately learned
methods of killing their victims
that would please
their twisted audience.
Kill or be killed.
At some point, they
must've just accepted it.
Their innocence long forgotten,
they descended into
the world of shadows.
[CHANG] Huh. Like a couple of
stunt dogs in the movies, huh?
Hmph. That's one
dark fairy tale.
But somehow fitting for
our world, wouldn't you say?
You know, sometimes,
I feel like I'm just wading
through a giant sea of shit.
Oh, well, "morality"
and "justice"
have never really suited me.
Words like that are
surprisingly similar
to the stuff that
comes outta your ass.
I have about as much
sympathy for those kids
as I do for people
who preach world peace
while they're dropping
bombs on their neighbors.
[BALALAIKA] I'm just telling
you what I know, Chang.
I don't think there's
any need for justice.
All we really need
is profit and trust.
[CHANG] Hmm...
Once we got to Rowan,
the rest was easy.
I see. So, this was
the source, huh?
Having one of your own killed
does work as the perfect alibi.
[BALALAIKA] Those kids
were intended for show.
No one ever taught
them any manners.
All they know how to do is cause
trouble and spread disaster.
Your men just happened to
get caught in their wake.
Whatever the reason,
someone's gonna
hafta pay for this.
What is going on?!
Damn it!
All they had to do was
get rid of that Ivan bitch!
So, why the fuck am I up
to my neck in dead bodies?!
--Boss.
--[VERROCCHIO] Yeah?
Let's cut our losses
and get rid of 'em.
Uh... Well, if we stop now,
we could still make it look like
we were the ones who
got rid of these brats
that were causing
all the trouble, right?
We could do it now without
any questions being asked,
but if we wait...
[VERROCCHIO] When I want
your fucking opinion,
I'll ask you for it! Or maybe
you want my job, is that it?
[MORETTI] But, Boss,
they're too much to handle!
[VERROCCHIO] Oh. Well,
why didn't you just say so?!
"Too much to handle,"
are they?!
Why do you think I called those
brats here in the first place?!
[BALALAIKA] I think we're
long overdue for a little
housecleaning in this city.
[CHANG] I definitely wouldn't
miss those tiresome meetings.
Does this mean you're planning
to start another war?
[BALALAIKA] Personally, I prefer
the term "controlled conflict."
And no one can say we
don't have good reason.
So, you're telling me
this is a just war?
And since when has that
kind of thing mattered to you?
If it provides an excuse,
then it matters.
Though I could care less
whether it's just or not.
Join us or forget
about it. It's up to you.
Eh, what the hell.
It's not like I need to
consult Hong Kong on this.
In the end,
there's only one thing
you can trust in this world
and that's brute force.
Does this mean we'll get to see
you with a gun in hand again?
I'm looking forward
to it... baby.
I don't dislike getting in
the game once in a while.
But in my position,
it's not that simple.
It's a real drag.
Oh, and one other thing--
you can stop calling me "baby."
I won't lie, I hate
that nickname.
[phone ringing]
[BORIS] Kapitän .
Sergeant, Chang has
agreed to our proposal.
As of right now,
we'll be fighting alongside
the Hong Kong Triad.
[BORIS] Roger.
[BALALAIKA] Get a message
to our fellow comrades.
Standby for combat
as of 19:05.
I predict Regulation 217,
case number five.
Do you copy, Sergeant?
[BORIS] Assumed
combat from 19:05.
You predict a snatch mission
within the city's
controlled battlegrounds.
[BALALAIKA] Correct.
I also predict chaos.
With all the bounty
hunters in town,
it's like Mardi Gras
down there.
[BORIS] It's better for us
that it is lively, Kapitän .
Nothing provides cover
like the sound of gunfire.
[BALALAIKA] You're right
about that, Sergeant.
We can justify this one attack,
but not a full-scale war.
Let's make it count.
[VERROCCHIO] Let me
tell you something else
I bet you don't know--
the bosses from Palermo
have actually shown some
interest in this damn,
backwards piece-of-shit city!
[gasping]
Now they're starting to
question my leadership
'cause I haven't been
able to take control!
All you useless bastards
better listen up!
Unless I do something
about it now,
what happens to me at the
next meeting of the families?
Take a guess!
--Damn it!
--[MAFIA MAN] Um... Um, Boss?
--[VERROCCHIO] Fuck off!
--It's just... that...
...the twins...
Why, those little bastards...
Hey... I-I thought I told
you two never to come here!
Wh-What the f--What the hell
are you doing?!
[giggling]
The two of us talked it over
and made a decision.
You did, did ya?!
[HANSEL] Yes. We'll have
borscht for our main course.
But we're going to start
with the macaroni. Okay?
[giggling]
Now... Now you've done it,
you damn brats! That's it!
I think our macaroni
just boiled over.
[HANSEL giggling]
Fuckin' bastards!
It's time for you to die!
[giggling]
Hmm...
[CHO] Dai-low Chang.
We now have the building
completely surrounded.
We're ready to move in
on your order.
Huh.
--Cho.
--Yes?
If I were you, I would
duck right about now.
Huh?
[glass shattering]
[smashing sound]
Looks like this job
just turned into a hunt.
[gunfire and screaming]
Get Hotel Moscow on the line.
They're gonna owe
me for this one.
[EDA] Revy, the cops
are on the move.
Looks like half
the force is here.
They're setting up
a roadblock behind me.
Apparently, it's
the Verrocchio family.
Something happened
at their place.
Revy! Are we just gonna sit and
watch this from the sidelines?!
[REVY] I know. Now can you
stop shouting in my ear?
So, where are we meeting up?
[EDA] Joey got a room
at the Palcana Square.
Now hurry your ass up!
Ah!
[DUTCH] Shit.
The fuse is lit and away we go.
There ain't no stopping it now.
All units, attention!
[BALALAIKA] Comrades.
Earlier tonight,
there was an assault
on the Verrocchio family.
However, this changes nothing.
We commence our mission
right here and now!
My brave comrades.
As you know, Private Sakharov
and Corporal Menshov
were irreplaceable
brothers in arms.
It falls to us to light
the candles for their souls!
Let our guns rain down
a terrible vengeance
upon their killers!
Our Kalashnikovs
will be their judge!
We'll tear apart their flesh
with the gunfire of our AK-74s!
[VISOTONIKIS] Yeah!
[gunfire and screaming]
[CHO] Dai-low Chang. I got
a message from Hotel Moscow
saying it's not
safe for us here.
They're recommending
that we pull out... now.
Huh. That's pretty clever.
[CHO] Uh...
In any case, it's too late now.
--And Cho... duck.
--Huh?
Get down!
[GRETEL giggling]
Not bad! You're good at this!
Well, thank you, young lady!
Unfortunately, I won't have
the time to deal with you today.
Haha! Maybe some other time.
Why doesn't that
put me at ease?
[police sirens]
[JOEY] The fire was
at the Verrocchio place.
It sounds like Watsap
is questioning the Triad
about it right now.
I'd say this route just
got closer to the gold.
[MAN 1] Opening night fireworks
are about to begin!
Hallelujah!
[MAN 2] Listen. It's a
black sedan, Japanese make.
[MAN 3] If they ditch the car,
we have no way of
knowing who they are.
[JOEY] Big fuckin' deal.
I'm shooting anyone I see.
[MAN 2] Hey, don't push!
Revy.
--Come here.
--[REVY] Huh?
What is it, Eda?
I just realized something.
Take a look around.
Whaddya mean?
Stop beating around
the fuckin' bush.
[EDA] It's Balalaika.
She's got the biggest score
to settle with those two brats,
but I'm looking around
and I don't see her here.
Yeah, now that
you mention it...
Right? If this was really
where it's gonna go down,
we would've been shut
out of the area by now.
So, where would the twins go?
Well, they're just
a couple of dumb fucks.
But if they have a target,
it has to be Balalaika.
Anyone else was a diversion.
Or just people
who got in the way.
Balalaika deployed
the Visotoniki
so she could get the
kids to come to her.
She'll kill them herself.
But the thing about soldiers
is they're pragmatic.
They won't act on speculation.
The brats will look
for a blind spot.
[EDA] These idiots must
think this is a deer hunt
in Montana or something.
But these are no deer.
These twins are coyotes.
They won't be easy prey.
Yeah. If they were stupid enough
to fall for a trap like this,
they'd be rotting under
a tombstone by now.
[EDA] For someone
with no education,
you catch on pretty quick, Revy.
So, whaddya think?
What's the fastest route
from here to Hotel Moscow?
We're gonna hafta
use backstreets.
We'll cut through
Chalquam Market
and then it's just straight
down Saatanam Street.
But more importantly,
last time I checked,
you had no education either,
you fuckin' whore.
[BALALAIKA] I'm sorry
for your loss, Chang.
[CHANG] 'Preciate it.
If I'd known
those kids were
gonna be in there,
I would've brought my
best shooters with me.
Thanks to them,
I have to walk home now.
Perfect end to a perfect night.
Oh, I took care
of Watsap for you.
I figured you could do without
him getting in the way.
So, I gave him a tip and sent
him off on a wild goose chase.
I'll let you figure
out how to pay me back.
Shrewd as always, Chang.
I definitely owe
you one for that.
Everything's going
according to plan.
Things should be getting
started any time now.
[tires squealing]
[MAN 1] There it is!
That's the car!
[MAN 2] No mistakin' it.
Black sedan, Japanese make.
Are the twins inside?
I can't tell with
those tinted windows!
I'm not waiting to find out!
Let's blow 'em away!
[MAN 5] Ow! You bastard!
You can go to hell!
[car horn]
[MAN 6] Did we get 'em?
[MAN 7] Hold up!
That kid ain't white!
[MAN 8] Those are a couple
of local kids! Damn it!
[MAN 9] We missed them! Fuck!
--[MAN 10] Shit!
--[MAN 11] Aw, fuck!
Watsap's headed south
for some fishing port.
[MAN 12] That's where they are!
--[MAN 13] Smoke 'em out.
--[MAN 14] C'mon!
[MAN 15] Get the car!
[HANSEL] I'm glad we decided
to do that, sora mea .
And since it only
cost 5,000 baht,
we didn't even have
to spend much money!
[GRETEL] That's true, but I
do feel kinda sorry for him.
He said he was an orphan.
[HANSEL] It's not
our fault though.
It's either kill or
be killed, remember?
That's what this
world is all about!
You're right, fratele meu .
It wasn't our fault.
[HANSEL] You see?
So, c'mon, let's go kill.
Let's keep killing.
[VISOTONIKI 1] Enemy located.
[BORIS] The team stationed
behind Chalquam Street
has engaged the enemy.
They're now attempting
to divert them.
[BALALAIKA] Good.
In which direction
are the kids headed?
Heading east, as planned.
They should be reaching
Ladoga Point any minute now.
[VISOTONIKI 2]
Target has gone left.
[BALALAIKA] No surprises.
They're going the way we want.
[BORIS] Unit Three engaged them
at Ladoga Point and they were
able to successfully divert
them towards Livinsk.
All units standby.
[BALALAIKA] I need
a unit stationed
at Hamipon Street immediately.
[BORIS]
Right.
We only want to leave
them one exit.
Have all squads fall back
after they've completed
their assignments.
Their objective is
to guide the enemy.
[distant bang]
Which team was that?
None of our troops are
stationed in that area.
It could be a bounty hunter.
All units report back.
Eliminate any interference.
[EDA] Hold it. Don't move
a muscle, you little brats.
You know, it's not
safe for kids
to be roaming the streets
this late at night.
Especially when the
entire city is on a manhunt
and you happen
to be the prize.
I guess neither of you have
been saying your prayers lately.
No, it's okay.
Hey! Can I ask
you a question?
How much are we worth?
What's the bounty being
offered on our heads?
Uh... Eighty grand. Don't move!
Wow. That's pretty good!
If you don't mind, I'd like
to discuss something with you.
You see, I have all this money
here from Verrocchio's office.
I don't mind fighting
you here if I have to,
but we still have some
things that we want to do.
Will you accept a hundred
thousand dollars
and pretend you
never saw us?
Ha! Get the fuck outta here.
I'm not getting
played by some kid!
[GRETEL] What about
one hundred and fifty?!
Huh?
Well?
Ah...
Um... Well, I...
What are we supposed
to do, Revy?!
[REVY] How is that
even a question?
The eighty grand, the one
hundred and fifty grand,
and their lives!
No reason we can't
take them all, right?!
[BORIS] We've confirmed
the target's position.
The Chinese woman
from Lagoon Company,
and the sister from the
Ripoff Church are there, too.
They have nothing to
do with our operation.
You may crush
them if necessary.
[GRETEL] It's the smell
of blood and rotten sewers.
It's because you and I
are the same thing!