Look, Lieutenant,
why do you think
we let that little bitch live?
I mean, c'mon!
Stop screwing around, man!
What? You think you're Paladin
from Have Gun Will Travel?
You just want that
poontang all to yourself?
Dontcha?
Hey, that's cool.
If you wait your turn,
maybe I'll letcha--
You're worse than a fucking
animal, you sick son of a bitch.
You're not gonna lay one
finger on her, you hear me?!
Bring it on.
If you've got the balls.
Hotel Quebec?
This is Sierra Niner.
Morales has just pulled up.
He's heading for
the hall.
Copy that.
Hotel Quebec? This is Lima Four.
Everything's set for Phase 3.
Santa Anna has taken his seat.
Same for
Morales and Sesma.
Copy that.
Hotel Quebec orders
all surveillance teams to
vacate the area and
regroup at the rendezvous point.
All units, this is
Hotel Quebec here.
You may proceed, Golf One.
Davy Crockett says Lone Star.
I repeat: Davy Crockett
says Lone Star.
Release code: check.
Target neutralized.
Right, let's bug out.
And no screw-ups.
He was a beloved father
and a treasured friend.
He protected the
weak and the helpless
Father was a good man. He
didn't do anything bad! Did he?
The Master has a place
in Heaven waiting for him.
May he rest in eternal peace.
There was no shame in
the way he lived his life.
So why, why would
God do this? Why?!
It was not God.
There is no greater killer
of man... than man himself.
Don't they feel anything?
How can people do
something like this?!
I know the answer
to that. I know it too well!
And that's why
I can never tell you!
You can come out, Rosarita.
They're leaving now.
Sorry about the trouble.
I will leave as
soon as the sun goes down.
Don't be in such a rush.
My best friend's daughter
has clearly travelled a long,
hard road and it would
dishonor my family name
if I didn't show
her some hospitality.
We should sit
for a while and talk.
Maybe even discuss your future.
Sound good?
I think running for your life
through the mountains
can wait in my opinion.
Senor Diego?
Sorry, just doing some chores.
It's such a
beautiful day I thought
I would do a
little gardening.
Why? You should
leave that to the gardener.
Yes, but this old
manor no longer has any staff.
In that case, Senor,
where should I start?
No, that's okay. You're
my guest, you should relax.
It would be unseemly to
spend a day without working.
To look like a maid and do
nothing would pain my heart.
At least treat me as if I were
truly a servant of the family.
Look at these, Roberta.
What are they? Is there some
significance to these guns?
These weapons have
been in our family since
the very first Lovelace
landed on the shores
of the New World
with Francisco Pizarro.
They've been with us
through good times and bad,
but seeing them just slumbering
like this makes the days
when we forged our family
motto seem long ago, indeed.
"A blessing for the living."
"A branch of
flowers for the dead."
"With a sword for justice."
And "The punishment of
death for the villains."
Those are just words.
Young Master.
I had to hold my tongue, I
wanted to tell you the truth,
but it's just too cruel!
Forgive me!
What did they feel
when they killed him?
They felt nothing.
There was no need for them
to even harden their hearts.
For one simple reason.
Because they had
emptied themselves
of all emotion to begin with.
His death was nothing to them.
It was just a
matter of routine.
This is a path
I've travelled before.
If I am to burn
in Hell, then so be it.
But neither the Master,
nor the Young Master,
should suffer for my sins!
Young Master...
Since that night in
that cesspool, Roanapur,
I believed I would
never pull another trigger.
I won't dignify
this by calling it revenge.
This is about dogs
tearing at each other!
I swear by Santa Maria, I
shall seek out those mongrels,
and rip out their throats!
The NSA have
been real cocksuckers
about this whole affair.
It's obvious they're horning
in on our territory here.
Do you know where
that unit was based
before heading to Roanapur?
Manila, for chrissake.
Goddamn them. Why do
they want to shit in the
nice little garden
we've been growing out there?
Cathy, another cup!
And add enough milk
and sugar to make pancakes!
I'm putting
Dr. Kaufman on the line.
Okay, then.
Well, my fellow spooks.
The game is all about getting
as much as you can
without starting a war.
And that's how it's played.
I am reporting live from
the scene of the crime downtown.
Anything new?
No, everything's still the same.
The borders with
Laos are still closed.
They're on full alert.
And considering our
issues with the Thai Air Force,
an air insertion is a negative.
So we have to stay on standby.
We're messing around in
the CIA's backyard, Major.
This is all about politics now.
Give me a fuckin' break.
...to the bank patrons as a
result of police fire
are still unse...
What's the name of
this place, Ray?
Sir?
Where the hell are we?
Ah! This is Roanapur, Major.
It's a real shithole.
First fucking day here,
seven of the men
had their pockets picked.
The whores are
right out on the street,
and the damn police
are their best customers!
All this gutter trash.
You know what it reminds me of?
Yeah, I know
what you're thinking.
'Nam, sixty-nine. Saigon. I'll
never forget that fuckin' smell.
Look, a Japanese businessman.
What?
Well there's a
fish out of water.
Jesus Christ. It's hotter
than hell out there
and he's still wearing
a dumb-assed necktie.
You see that?
He doesn't even
know he just got robbed.
Hey! What do you
think you're doing, you?!
You know who
I am, motherfucker?
Uh... the Lagoon crew.
The dumb dipshit who
owns this wallet is with us.
See, we got a
reputation to think of.
Teach your little bum-boys
about the food chain here.
Now beat it. Fuck off.
Uh. If this is about
your payment, we could use--
We don't believe
in working on credit.
We only made
an exception because
the Columbian Cartel
vouched for you.
Be careful you
don't dishonor their name.
Ah well, this isn't
the best place to talk.
It's a bit noisy here,
but maybe we can, uh--
Oh! Sounds like
the game just ended.
Please, come on in.
I'll pass. But you
should know that there's
a stone-cold killer behind me.
And she's got you in her sights.
I see, uh... We'll
have the money tomorrow.
Tomorrow, then.
Rock.
You should have let the
street urchin keep the money.
It's not like I
have a lot leftover
from my paycheck anyway.
Because you're
such a fuckin' softie,
the brat would go
after even fatter wallets.
Before too long, he'd be
a floater in the river.
Dumbass.
You just blindly want
to help people out, don't ya?
You know, people
like the girl in the
photo you've
got stuffed in here.
You looked?
Yeah, I peeked inside.
A bullet never hits
you in the same place twice.
If I told you it's a good luck
charm, would you believe me?
Give me a fuckin' break, Rock.
This is gettin' to be a habit.
The skeletons on the
U-boat. The Romanian twins.
And then that Yakuza's daughter.
You did your best
to help them and in the end
your half-assed efforts were
completely fucking
pointless, Rock.
"Pointless" is
this city's motto.
"Come to beautiful Roanapur,
we have a coffin
waiting just for you."
God, I love this place.
Lagoon Company.
Yeah... Hmm...
And why do you wanna know?
Beats me. I'm just
the messenger boy.
The Chief just told
me to call you up and ask.
Fine. Damn it.
We in trouble?
Nope. I was asked if we'd
had an unusual visitor yet.
Again? That's just creepy!
They keep calling us!
Everyone from Isaac,
the fence down by the docks,
to Watsap at the police station
is obsessed with a visitor
we haven't even seen yet.
Who the hell
are they talking about?
I just heard
the most fucked up news.
It's from Kowalski
at Hotel Moscow.
What?
He said he saw
her here in town.
Who, his mother?
The maid, Dutch. The one
with the shitload of weapons
who came all the way here
from some ass-pit in Venezuela.
You know, to rescue
that little prick we kidnapped.
The four-eyed,
fuckin' super terrorist.
Well, this is
a kick in the balls.
Ain't it? Look Revy, I wanna
find out what's going on fast,
before I get blown up. I'm
gonna check out a few places.
We'll meet at the Yellow Flag.
Well, our mystery
guest has checked in.
Yeah?
Damn, what a pain.
Aw, hell. This bar has
been trashed fifteen times
since seventy-eight, and
completely destroyed six times!
And the last shit-storm
when that killing machine
disguised as a
fucking maid showed up
was the worst one of all!
That's a sad story.
But you shouldn't worry
about crap you can't control.
I asked all the women upstairs,
but they were clueless.
Let me know
if shit goes down.
Sure.
So the Triad is searching
for the maid as well?
It's like the whole city
has got a hard-on for her.
Heh. Another group.
Columbians, this time.
Yo, Gustavo!
Hey, a couple of Lagoon's crew.
Where's Senor Abrego?
The boss is
holed up in the office,
we got a little situación.
Soldiers from the
head office are coming,
but we don't have
any more room for them,
it's a big pain
in the ass, I tell you.
But you know I think blessed
Maria must love me today!
I wanted to talk
to you about something.
Lemme guess.
About the maid, right?
You just said
you're getting soldiers
straight from the head office.
Now what else would you
be fuckin' talking about?
Jesus, wipe that look
off your face, wouldja?
We'd be happy to
talk to you for some intel!
Or fuck off.
You have our word we
won't leak this, fair enough?
Puta madre!
But you two
are gonna go first!
All right.
So where do we start?
None of us
actually saw the bitch
the last time she came in here.
What's she look like?
Her personality?
Any unique shit.
She has black hair. She's
Hispanic with pale skin.
I hear she's
dressed like a waitress?
She's fucking nuts.
She has a SPAS-12 umbrella
and enough small arms
and grenades in her case
to outfit an
entire rifle company.
Fuck me, this sounds bad!
I told you, remember?
She's bat-shit crazy.
Is... Is this
some kind of joke?
The Lagoon Company's
office seems to be
closed at the moment.
And The Young Master
talked of this establishment,
so I came here on my search.
The Young Master is waiting
at the Sankan Palace Hotel.
Please go to him
immediately. Right now.
Uh. Excuse me, but
are you with the Lovelaces?
Oh, pardon me. I am a
maid for the Lovelace family,
one of the thirteen
great families of South America.
My name is Fabiola Iglesias.
I hate her! She talks just
like that bitch in glasses.
I beg your pardon, but
you shouldn't be calling our
head maid a "bitch in glasses."
Please take that back.
Hermano, is this that maid?
No, man! But fuck
are we ever lucky!
This little puta just gave
us the clue we were looking for.
This kid is heavy, real heavy.
This article came up
when I started my search.
Last October terrorists set off
a bomb in Barinas, Venezuela.
In South America, that's
like talking about the weather.
Their target was a
political party, the MVR.
A new organization.
They were popular with the poor,
but the elites
weren't too fond of them.
Problem is the
Lovelace patriarch
was also taken
out in that explosion.
Holy shit.
He may have been one
of the elites, but in fact,
he was pretty
liberal in his thinking.
But it still doesn't add up.
What does any of that
have to do with Roanapur?
Alright, Mini-maid,
how about you start talking,
cuz we're all real
big fans of your head maid.
My apologies, but I
don't know where she is myself.
Then why don't we go look
for her together, little chica?
And we'll start with
that Sankan Palace Hotel.
I have been careless.
From the foul
stench I knew this town
would be filled with animals.
But then our
family's mortal enemies
have always
smelled like dirty pigs.
I got her, hermano!
We can go now?
Que?
F-Fucking little puta!
She stabbed me in the cojones!
Hey, no guns
allowed in-- okay.
She's not just some
fucking housekeeper!
She's like that other bitch!
Aw, now you've
drawn your weapons.
I was hoping to avoid this.
Hidalgo!
Right here, boss!
Frisk that little bitch!
And be fucking careful!
Who the hell knows what
this loca puta is packing.
Let's roll.
Ah, shit!
She's using buckshot!
Be careful!
Dammit, Revy, you started this!
Calm down, ya pussy!
I need the phone!
Hey, don't come back here!
Asshole!
Uh-oh... Benny!
You know, this is just a guess
but, I think it'll be tough
to get a drink
at the Flag tonight.
Yeah. But I bet the place
is gonna to be well-ventilated.
Give it some gas!
Hang on!
She's pretty good alright!
Hey, Boss, we're here!
Light this fucking place up!
No, you shitheads!
Open fire now!
The maid's in here!
The maid!
Marrero! Shoot the bar!
That psycho's in there!
Give her hell!
It's just like Roberta
said! A terrible city!
Listen to me, you cowards!
Your friends out there
really don't care about you!
You are nothing to them!
Live or die, what'll it be?!
Now gather your
wounded and get the hell out!
Retreat! Retreat!
Honestly, this place
is a rat's nest.
You're dead!
Hey, asshole. I think
it's time to hit the showers.
Crazy bitches!
Mr. Chang, it appears the
Colombians are falling back.
There's nothing to be gained
from us rushing over there now.
Especially if the stories
about the maid's past are true.
Do you think this is all
about revenge for her master?
Makes sense, Boss.
I just feel like I'm
pissing into the wind here.
Uh, Sir?
What I mean is, why can't we
track down this maid
everyone is talking about?
There's a stranger
hiding somewhere in my city.
And I hate that.
I'm a little speechless.
Does everyone in your
house dress for a small war?
So cool!
Oh no, it's just
the head maid and me.
So altogether, there are five
of us on the household staff
right now, but none of the other
maids know that I carry guns.
I was hired to ensure
the Young Master was
never left unprotected
when the head maid
was away from the manor.
Sankan Palace. It doesn't
get much ritzier than this.
Wish I could
afford to stay here.
Allow me to remind you...
You'll be in the presence of
Master Garcia Fernando
Lovelace, the twelfth head
of the Lovelace
family, one of the
thirteen Great Families
of South America...
The Lagoon crew at last.
What took you so long?
Oops.
Easy cutie,
let's just keep our cool.
Fabiola, the gentleman is only
here to talk. He gave his word.
Be on your guard. This city is
filled with the vilest of scum.
Sorry to interrupt.
You want us to come in or what?
Yes, of course.
Please come in!
Before we begin...
Revy, ask for permission
before you light up that smoke.
Are you shittin' me?
Like I'm gonna ask him!
Revy.
Oh for-- All right then.
Uh, so listen, kid.
May I please enjoy my
hard-earned tobacco product?
We have no ashtrays here.
Please save it for later.
Jesus.
Following my father's death,
the members of a right wing
militia group were arrested.
Take out the leaders of
the leftist opposition
party with a bomb?
Sounds reasonable enough.
Hmm, it's so clean and
logical that it can't be legit.
Roberta felt the same.
They lacked the expertise to
pull off that kind of operation,
and there was no need for it.
But the police were acting
as if the case was closed.
That's how things stood
until the day some officers
from the airborne
regiment came to my house.
The Fifth Republic
Movement known as the MVR.
The party was founded by
Venezuelan airborne officers.
A lot of leftists in that unit.
They came to tell me about
the investigation
they'd been conducting.
And how they'd reviewed the
staff records for the ceremony.
Some men vanished
immediately after the bombing.
So they did a full
background check on them.
And hit a bull's eye.
Yes. The names
of six of those men
popped up in
other records as well.
They'd been members of
a foreign intelligence agency.
And, as if pre-planned,
they'd all resigned
from active duty
two months ago.
The day of the
bombing they were all
on the security
detail guarding the stage.
Shit, that's just retarded!
Keeping their old identities
like that is such
sloppy fuckin' work.
Go home and
jerk off or whatever,
because four-eyes will be right
back after she massacres 'em.
Fabiola, the photo.
Yes, sir.
Take a look at this.
The officers also provided
us with this photograph.
This was in Caracas six
months before the bombing.
While looking into
a case of embezzlement,
military investigators
just happened to
get a picture of them.
The man on the far right,
Major Marcos Lucientes,
is the leader
of the six conspirators.
He's a foreign
intelligence operative.
And the others?
They're not Venezuelan.
After she saw that,
Roberta seemed different.
Young Master. Do you remember
that night in Roanapur?
Of course I do. The Columbian
Cartel tried to sell me
like I was a piece of meat.
And then you crossed the ocean
and saved me from them!
You did so much for me.
When you were taken
from us, Master Diego tried to
prevent me
from going after you,
but in the end,
there was no choice.
If he had--
I understand.
If it had been me
instead of my father.
I would have
tried to stop you, too.
Yes. The two of you
are from another time.
Roberta, stay.
Not to worry, Young Master.
Know that wherever you are,
I shall always be at your side.
But the next day,
she was gone.
Dammit, who the hell is she?
Mendes, it's me!
Someone is on my tail.
Hurry and get
over here right away--
I am afraid that
Mendes is unable to
answer the
phone at the moment.
What the--? Who is this?!
Shouldn't the question be, "How
did you get his cell phone?"
Isn't that what
you should be asking?
And I have more
than just Mendes' phone.
But they couldn't help me.
It appears that
you are the only one
who can answer
all of my questions.
They found Jose
Lucientes' body in a canal
on the outskirts of Calabozo.
She was able to
identify and track him down
from a single photo?
Impressive, I can
see how she earned
the nickname "Bloodhound."
Uh...
She is not a bloodhound!
She's my family!
A thousand pardons,
Senor Garcia. Let us resume.
Yes. Back to
the business at hand.
Her next target was
the second man from the right.
I'm important!
Do you have any idea who I am?
Yes, I do. You're with the NSA,
America's National
Security Agency.
You're Colonel Simon Dickens,
a specialist in Central America
and the officer in
charge of a unique program
that conducts policy
analysis in the region.
Jesus Christ, so you've
done your homework.
What do you want?!
According to the late
Marcos Jose Lucientes,
you and your men were
responsible for planning
and carrying out the
terrorist bombing attack
in Caracas, Venezuela
last October.
No! You wouldn't!
I want to know
where your hounds are.
You should start talking
before you begin to cook.
It would save us
both a lot of time.
Don't... don't do this,
you fucking psycho bitch!
If you kill me you're gonna have
every single American agency
gunning for your
crazy fuckin' ass!
I'm waiting.
Colonel Dickens' body was
found in the burned out ruins
of a building in
a suburb of Caracas.
The main suspect is
a woman who inquired about
buying a ticket from
Venezuela to Thailand via Miami.
She also made a reservation
for a long-distance bus to
take her from
the airport to Roanapur.
She went after a
United States Army colonel?
You're sure about that?
Yes.
Sorry, kid, this
sounds like a real mess.
So what'd ya want from
us besides fuckin' sympathy?
I need some help.
Fuckin' motherfuckin' fucks!
What's wrong, Bao?
You remodeling again?
Shuddup!
If you assholes wanna drink,
then I got the booze.
Hey, you. Do I look
like I'm fuckin' open?
If you're here to tease--
War is coming.
I can see why you're so
nervous about this, Chang.
You can't pay us enough.
We're gonna sit this one out.
No, why?!
Don't ya get it? Your head maid
has just declared a showdown
with everyone's favorite
buddy, the U.S. of fucking A.
Sorry, what'd ya just say?
I want to know the locations
of all the nearby shops
that carry
weapons and ammunition.
There is a war coming.
Every corner of this
city is filled with people
who struggle
against overwhelming odds
and fail and are
now just waiting to die.
We're not interested
in hiring your company.
That is not why
I came looking for you.
We're hiring him.
The Japanese man there.
Hold on. Do you mean me?
You do! Now wait a minute!
Why do you want me?!
Our head maid is
somewhere in this city.
Please help us find her!
I know this is a lot
to ask of you. But, please!
You want me?! You're both nuts!
If you are the gun,
then I am the bullet.
But I am nothing more
than a simple chunk of lead.
To fire the gun,
you need gunpowder.