Roberta.
Get down! Both of you!
[ROCK] Get outta the way!
[GARCIA] No! Please
don't shoot Roberta!
If this could kill her,
we wouldn't be in
this fuckin' mess.
[GARCIA] Roberta!
[horn honking]
Oh, shit!
Damn it!
Dutch! We're off the main road!
We're headed right
for the ocean.
There's nowhere to go.
It's a dead end.
Shit, we're screwed!
No!
[crow cawing]
It pays to be a
religious man, after all.
All survivors, speak up.
Somehow, we're both alive.
[DUTCH] What about Revy?
[ROCK] She never even woke up.
Still knocked out.
You okay, Benny?
[BENNY] You've
gotta be kidding!
What the hell's
this woman made of?
[REVY] Damn it.
Revy.
Fucking hell. Hey, what
happened to that stupid bitch?
She dead yet? Well?
You're in luck.
She's alive and well.
[REVY] Well, that's the
best news I've heard all day.
I've got an errand to run.
Wait! Revy!
[REVY] Listen closely, Rock.
I'm about to light up
like a goddamn firecracker
and there's nothing
anyone can do about it.
When that happens,
it's pretty much over.
I'm not even gonna warn you
before I give you
a second asshole.
When she decided to
use that shell on me,
she made a big fuckin' mistake.
I'm gonna make that bitch
wish she was still home,
cleaning shitty toilets.
It's time to go teach
this fucking cunt
the meaning of pain.
[sirens in distance]
Make a move, señorita .
Or are you scared?
You fuckin' should be.
[ROBERTA] I have no
need for filthy language
and idle threats.
You will not find me
so easily intimidated.
Knowing you could not
defeat me with skill alone,
you chose to hide behind
the young master instead.
You are a coward.
[DUTCH] Rock, watch out
for stray bullets.
I can't see them.
They just disappeared.
[gunshot in distance]
Roberta.
[gunfire]
Oww... Damn it.
Somehow, she managed to put
a bullet in the great Revy.
Who the fuck is this woman?
I'm no shrink, but you must've
had one fucked up childhood.
Where'd you come from?
Tell me!
[seagulls]
I get it now.
I thought I knew that smell
lingering around you.
I'd recognize that
scent anywhere.
It's the smell of gutter mud
still clinging to your feet.
It's perfect, really.
All the more reason why
we need to finish this off.
[birds chirping]
[ROBERTA] I can't go back.
I can never return there now.
Roberta!
Now...
What's the plan?
I suppose we should try
to get outta this car.
Whaddya think?
Uh... Yeah, you're right.
Roberta!
How?
It's impossible, alright.
We'd never make it no matter
how many lives we had.
I'm not about to go
anywhere near that fight.
[BENNY] Amen!
You know what they say--
there's an end to
every beginning.
I'm sure they'll
settle this eventually.
Hey, kid! Whadda you doing?
Garcia, wait.
Roberta!
You can win!
Don't you let that
woman beat you!
Sounds like the gunfire
is getting closer.
[REVY] This bitch! I'll kill
her! I swear I'll kill her!
[ROBERTA] I'm gonna
send you straight to Hell!
[BALALAIKA] Osta-noh-vee-tish!
[don't move]
Why don't you call it
quits now, you two?
Neither one of you
stands to gain anything
from continuing this battle.
So, stop wasting your
energy, Two-Hands.
Shut up.
I'm gonna kill this bitch.
[BALALAIKA] There's something
you should probably know,
Miss Maid.
Hotel Moscow has
been planning a war
against the Manisarela
Cartel for some time,
so imagine my surprise.
Taking care of this one was
actually supposed to be my job,
but you came along and
saved me the trouble.
As we speak, their
headquarters in Venezuela
should be in ruins.
Therefore, all of our problems
have now been solved.
Garcia's kidnapping has also
been dealt with and he may go.
So, you have no
reason to fight, do you?
Those are no doubt the
three most terrifying
women in the world.
This feels way too
much like Ground Zero.
It doesn't matter.
Indeed.
Is that so?
Don't misunderstand me, ladies.
That's not just some
friendly suggestion.
It's an order.
[ROCK] Who are those guys
and where did they come from?
They don't seem like they're
just ordinary Russian mafia.
Those uniforms...
Are they military?
Roberta!
You don't have
to worry, Roberta!
Look at me! I'm fine!
They never even hurt me!
Please. Let's go home!
This has to stop.
I don't wanna see you
with a gun anymore.
I don't want you to kill.
I agree, kid. You're right.
But...
...what does the Bloodhound
think about that?
Bloodhound?
Oh... so no one ever
bothered to tell you?
--Well...
--You shut up!
[BALALAIKA] I suggest
you keep quiet, bitch.
Let me tell you...
I'm not sure what you think,
but this isn't just some servant
who looks good walking the dog.
She's the Bloodhound
of Florencia.
Rosarita Cisneros.
Trained as an assassin in Cuba,
she's a former
FARC guerilla.
She's wanted internationally
for multiple
kidnappings and murders.
And she's a suspect in the
bombing of the US embassy
in Tegucigalpa.
She's a real hardcore terrorist.
[GARCIA] Roberta...
Is it true?
[ROBERTA] I swear
that I never intended
to deceive you, Master Garcia.
However, there are things...
There are some things
in this world
that it's better not to know.
They bring only sadness.
Everything she said
is the truth.
I... I believed in it
with all my heart.
I believed in the
dawn of a revolution
that would bring justice
to this world at last.
For that reason and
that reason alone...
...I became a soldier.
In the blind pursuit
of this ideal,
I killed in every
place imaginable.
Politicians, businessmen,
counter-revolutionaries,
election officials.
I even killed women
and children.
So many of my nights
stained with blood...
Countless mornings spent
feeling cold and empty,
and what I realized in the end
was that I was
no revolutionary.
I was nothing more
than a guard dog
working for the mafia, helping
to protect their coca fields.
Isn't it ironic?
The revolutionaries
working side by side
with the cartels.
They said revolution would not
be possible with ideals alone.
And in saying that,
they'd already sold their
souls and I knew it was over.
My only option was
to leave the military.
And there was just one
man I could think of
who would agree
to take me in.
A close friend of
my deceased father.
The man who saved me was
none other than your father,
Master Diego Lovelace.
Master Garcia,
allowing your
kidnapping to happen
was negligence on
my part. I failed you.
And then I knew of no other
way to save you except to
awaken a side of myself that
had long been hidden away.
A side of me that I
had abandoned long ago.
Bloodhound. Guard dog.
I've lived my
entire life as a dog.
And this is the only
way that I know
how to prove my
devotion to you.
I wanted to repay
you with my life.
No! How could you call
yourself a dog, Roberta?!
Don't believe in those lies!
We're a family,
aren't we, Roberta?!
So, how could you
ever say you're a dog?!
You're nothing like that!
It's just not true!
And I don't know
any Bloodhound!
She died a long time ago!
There's no more
Rosarita, either!
I bet she moved
somewhere far away
to try and hide from her sins!
Don't you see?!
That woman has got nothing
to do with you anymore!
The only one I see
here is my Roberta!
Young Master.
[GARCIA] So...
Let's go.
I... I just wanna
go back home now.
It's okay, Young Master.
Let me dry your eyes.
Boys should not cry so easily.
I'm glad that's settled.
We could've had a
big mess on our hands.
[REVY] Give me a fuckin' break.
I'm sure everybody
is just delighted
with this teary-eyed
happy ending.
Well, fuck that!
I'm not gonna pretend
to be happy about it.
What about this fuckin'
tunnel in my shoulder? Huh?
Couldn't you just let that go?
Come on now, Sis. We both
know that's not cool.
Even criminals have a code of
honor. We have to settle this.
You know that perfectly
well, Sis, so come on.
Hmm... Yes, you
do have a point.
Well, seems obvious to me.
A little bare-knuckle boxing
until they're satisfied.
Anyway, I doubt
that anyone will die.
Fine by me!
Young Master?
Don't you lose to
that woman, okay?
You're stronger
than her, Roberta!
Well, then I guess it's decided.
Go for as long as you want.
Fine.
I'm gonna make
you uglier, bitch.
But before we start,
your shoelace is untied.
She got one in!
Must be nice to be so young.
[REVY] Damn it!
Come on, Roberta!
Don't lose to her!
Who are you betting on?
I'm going with two on Revy.
Alright, then I'll hafta
go with three on Roberta.
You, Rock?
W-Wait a minute!
We should stop this, right?!
We can't let this go on!
Hm? Why not?!
[ROCK] Well...well,
it's completely barbaric!
Am I the only one
who sees this?
It's totally insane to have
two girls going at it like that!
Then why don't you
go and stop them?
You said you don't like this.
I did, but--
[BALALAIKA] Then get out
there and put a stop to it.
Really, don't worry
about it, we don't mind.
[ROCK] Umm...
Excuse me. Ladies?
Haven't you had enough
of this fighting?
Why not try this--sit down
and talk things through.
I'm sure you have more
in common than you thought.
--Stay the fuck out of this!
Or I could do that. Great idea.
[DUTCH] What did you expect?
[BALALAIKA] They just won't
give up. This is getting boring.
Why won't you die?
Die already, fuckin' four-eyes!
Same to you. W-Why the hell
won't you just go down?
Damn you! Take this, bitch!
There! It's a draw.
[GARCIA] Roberta!
Young Master...
I'm so sorry.
I should've beaten her.
[GARCIA] No, don't talk.
In the end, you were
the last one standing.
So... it's alright.
[chuckling]
[DUTCH] That's a terrible sight.
[ROCK] She's out cold.
Can you stand? Hang on to me.
[ROBERTA] I'm sorry.
Don't you say that, Roberta.
You want a hand
with her, Garcia?
[GARCIA] Leave us alone.
I don't need anyone's
help looking after her.
Roberta is a maid at my house.
So, it's my job to get her home.
Spoken like the
future patriarch.
--Comrade Sergeant.
--Ma'am.
Treat her wounds, then
take them to the airport.
If any remaining cartel
members attempt an attack,
dispose of them immediately.
Understood.
I have a favor
to ask, please....
What?
It's my glasses... Could you
go and pick them up for me?
Why?
I mean, they're just
fake, aren't they?
Yes.
However, I need them.
Those glasses help
me believe I'm her.
I just want to be your Roberta.
[ROCK] Hey! It's morning,
Revy! Wake up!
That barely registered.
I do not wanna be around when
she wakes up. Won't be pretty.
But...
...who were those
guys back there?
You know, all those guys
from the Russian mafia.
They were, like, military.
Actually, they're
ex-miliatry. You're close.
They were either paratroopers
or in the Special Forces.
Her immediate subordinates
have enough training
to fight and win World War III
if they wanted to.
They're pretty much
all Afghan vets
with an insane amount
of experience and skill.
She was the brains
of the operation
and these men became
unstoppable killing machines.
Eventually, these same guys
returned from that hell
of hot sand and carnage.
[ROCK] Everyone's
feet are covered
with mud from the gutter.
[CHANG] Five teams will leave
Roanapur at the same time
and each will have a completely
different destination.
There are five cases.