[ROCK] The sea's so calm today.
It's incredible!
The waters around here
can look like something
from an acid trip.
You dive in and it's pretty
much a sensory overload.
I'm sure it is.
I went scuba diving a while
back at Ishigaki Island.
Now that sounds privileged.
Like another exciting day in
the life of a yuppie bachelor.
It wasn't all that great.
Drinking this beer and feeling
the sea breeze on my face
is far more
privileged than that.
[harmonica]
So, this is "Farewell, Germany."
It's a shame that the last
glimpse I'm going to get
of the German sky is of
its usual leaden color.
Yes, but thanks to that,
the Allies' patrol
over us has thinned.
Once we're passed the
Shetlands and North Sea,
in no time, we'll be
under Spain's blue sky
and then on to
Africa's beaches.
You'll soon be longing
for some clouds,
Lieutenant Colonel Matsuto.
Right. As a man who came
here to study aeronautics,
I can hardly afford to be killed
by a plane at this point.
[CAPTAIN AHBE] Not after
coming all the way to Germany.
It seems that we'll get along
just fine on this journey.
But I wish I could say the same
about that other passenger.
[CAPTAIN AHBE] I just
don't understand them.
The SS and the SDs, those men,
they're a different breed.
[ROCK] Oh, man.
Now that I think about it,
maybe I did lead
a privileged life.
One little problem with
the car and all of a sudden,
life takes a major
turn for the worse here.
Mr. Lun, is that new? How much?
That's too high. It's
probably stolen, anyway.
Oh well, then. It's not like
anyone here has cash to spare.
I better pass. I can already see
Revy calling me a sucker again.
[seagulls]
Check.
[CAPTAIN AHBE] Gentlemen,
we can all look forward
to sea turtle soup tonight.
[men cheering]
[CREWMAN 1] They're moving
with us on a bearing of 2-7-0.
It's a freighter out of
South Africa heading to Ceylon.
Ah, Captain.
We are in battle
positions right now.
I'm afraid you'll
have to go inside.
I'm sorry for the intrusion,
but I have something
to ask, if I may.
Do you really plan to ignore
the orders you were given
and attack that freighter?
What shall we do?
I'll get you to Batavia without
fail, Lieutenant Colonel.
--Now, Fritz.
--Yes, sir.
Are you incapable of
even greeting the enemy
without confirmation?
And yet, you call yourself...
Very well, sir. I'll have them
hurry up and load the torpedo
that's under maintenance.
You too, Lieutenant Colonel.
Please get inside.
An attack would be
an unnecessary risk.
That transport belongs to
our sworn enemy--England.
What's being carried is fuel
to be used for an invasion
of our allies that
we'll soon be visiting.
And you're telling me
to ignore the enemy.
Are you saying there was no
point in us fighting this war?
That all those soldiers
died for nothing?
I am saying that at this
stage, sinking that ship
will have absolutely no
effect on our fatherland.
Hmph. Really?
What is it?
There's no point? We're just
fighting a losing battle here?
We can't stop the inevitable?
Are you trying to provoke
me into saying more?
No, I didn't
expect that from you.
I suppose I thought
you were worried
about something
much more insignificant.
I apologize. Despite that,
there are still some fights
that you must take on.
Let's go. Prepare the torpedoes
for surface attack.
We'll credit this ship
with her 31st hit.
[CREWMAN 2] Launcher is ready.
[CAPTAIN AHBE]
Alright, let's go.
We'll keep fighting
to the very end.
[DUTCH] Aren't you
going for a drink?
I'll go as soon as
I'm done calculating
the torpedo boat's
fuel efficiency.
[DUTCH] Atta boy.
What's all that?
I dunno. Do I look like
an off-season Santa to you?
Earlier today, you were looking
around in the shop, weren't you?
Huh? No, but...
Just tell me when
you want something.
Huh? Hold on. Then you're
saying that's for me?
[chuckling]
The enemy ship has
just passed over us.
Set course to 2-0-0. We need
to get behind the enemy.
If we turn twice, we'll be
able to achieve that, sir.
The second turn will
be in four minutes.
Very well. Then that's
what we'll go with.
We're detecting sound from
another vessel in front of us.
Wait, there's another signal.
It looks like the enemy's
coming out in numbers.
Batavia's right there in front
of us and we're being cornered.
Not yet, gentlemen. I want
both engines to full power.
--Set us to 1-7-0.
--[CREWMAN 3] 1-7-0!
Fire the Zigarren
directly astern.
[CREWMAN 2] Firing Zigarren!
One of the enemy
ships is moving away.
Then it must have worked.
They took the bait.
Now cut the engine. It's silent
running from now on.
One ship is staying
right with us.
[CREWMAN 2] They're using
their active sonar!
Full power! Twenty to port!
Dive to a depth of forty!
[alarm sounding]
This is the forward torpedo
room. We're taking on water.
Close the fore hatch! You can
still try to save yourselves!
[FRITZ] We are doing our best
to stop taking on water,
but we can't vent
the ballast tank.
Engines and the
emergency generator
are damaged beyond repair.
[CAPTAIN AHBE] It's
unfortunate that we couldn't
return our Japanese
passenger to his homeland.
Lieutenant Colonel Matsuto
has already...
The way of a samurai.
I didn't realize
he brought a sword
with him for that reason.
You've served as brave and loyal
sailors of the German Navy.
As a crew, we've
faced rough waters
and overcome great
opposition in the Atlantic,
but sadly, none of us will
leave this battle behind
for the beaches of Batavia.
Our ship has currently run
aground at a depth of 57 meters.
Both our engines and ballast
tank are beyond repair.
You have all endured numerous
battles and shown great courage.
As of now, I'm relieving you
of your military duties.
We are going to run out of
air in about two hours.
In these final moments, it is
your choice how you wish to die.
Lietenant Colonel,
I have to speak with you.
Captain,
I haven't heard the engine
running for some time now.
When are we going to surface?
As it turns out, we won't
be surfacing... ever again.
I'm truly sorry.
You are worthless.
I agree.
You don't get it! You just
don't understand, do you?!
Understand what?
The importance of your mission!
Do you have any idea
of the significance
of this painting
I'm transporting?
I see. So, the package
was this painting.
It doesn't look like anything
of great significance to me.
What is its title?
It's called "The Twelve
Knights Led by Brunhilda."
Listen to me carefully--what
I have in my hands right now
is the only tableau painted
since the Führer took power.
"Steadfast in our
honor and loyalty,
we shall keep this hidden
until the promised day.
On the day when the Nazi flag
flies victorious once again,
this will be a beacon
for all our comrades
who have scattered and
a call for reunification."
So, you've already resigned
yourself to the idea
that we're going
to lose this war.
And so you figured
you'd just start preparing
for the next one.
You people make me sick!
Do you have any family?
I have a wife and child. They
are in Stuttgard. So, what then?
You know, I can honestly say
I'm proud that I fought
to the very end for my country.
I have no regrets, even now
as I'm destined to rot here.
However, if there's one
dissatisfaction I do have,
it is the fact I must
share a casket
with some fucking
bastard like you,
who isn't even thinking about
his family in his dying moments.
Take back that
statement, Captain!
You cannot compare family
to the righteousness
of our country!
It's pointless.
You can deny it all you
want, but Hitler's empire
is crashing down around us
and there's nothing you can do.
Be quiet!
Look what's become
of my country
and my navy as a
result of putting up
with your delusions
for all these years.
Enough!
I'd even say it
was worth sinking
if it meant that my
children could grow up
without ever having to see
that accursed Nazi flag again.
Shut up! Take it back!
It could very well
be the will of God
that our boat sank here today.
[gunshots]
[ROCK] Damn it.
Why'd I have to go
and open my big mouth?
I've only been scuba diving once
in my life at Ishigaki Island.
Dutch tricked me into this.
That's the only thing you've
been saying since we left port!
Could you try to be a little
bit more interesting,
you blubbering idiot?
[ROCK] There's no way I'm gonna
be able to do this salvage.
Now, I explained this
briefly at the office,
but we'll go over the details
again before we go in.
Benny, will you start?
No problem. First of all,
let's take a look at this.
An old story from
half a century ago.
The nostalgic talk
of some old-timer.
IXC-type attack submarine
U-1324 of the German Navy.
It was a submarine in the wolf
pack that tore up the Atlantic.
The captain was
Major Venztel H. Ahbe.
The last order he ever received
from his falling homeland
was to take an officer of
the Japanese Navy to Batavia.
But things weren't
that simple for them.
They had to go
from Kiel in Europe,
around Cape Agulhas,
then through the Indian Ocean.
It's a voyage
worthy of Magellan.
And Ahbe managed to pull it off.
But when he was in plain
view of his destination,
his ship, all its crew members,
and the passengers on board
suddenly ran out of luck.
While searching
for the Japanese,
the US Navy came
across this U-boat.
Having nothing else to do,
all of them decided
to strike at once.
The poor U-1324
finally went down.
So, the captain and 44 of
his crew just disappeared
into the depths of the ocean.
That's sorta the history with
a capital "H" as we know it.
But there's another untold
story in all of this.
A story about an SS officer
who appeared at Kiel Port
the night before departure
and was able to
force his way on board
with papers from
the secret police.
Now check this out--
this is the painting
that SS officer
held on to for dear life.
The artist is August Janke,
an unknown painter.
Its title is "The Twelve
Knights Led by Brunhilda."
That thing looks
pretty boring to me.
I've seen graffiti
on New York subways
that would put that to shame.
Why would an SS officer board
a submarine with no gold,
no secret documents,
and only a single painting?
Don't give it too much thought.
It's just an incredible story.
I have no real explanation
for why it happened
or even where it came from.
However, the one thing we
are sure of right now is that
this painting is preserved
inside the wreck of a submarine.
We've been hired by an
antique collector in Spain.
And this guy's hobby happens
to be collecting Nazi artwork.
That's a pretty fucked up hobby.
Damn straight. Apparently
most of Janke's work
was destroyed or
lost in the war.
He'd completely given up on this
and the U-boat long ago, but...
Yeah. Last year,
a French telecom company
was laying down
underwater cables
and they inadvertently
discovered the U-1324.
At the same time, they found out
there wasn't much water inside.
Several countries
are in dispute
over the rightful ownership
of these waters,
so no one is able to
make a move for it easily.
And so, that's where
we come in, people.
Not bad for a fifty
thousand dollar job.
[BENNY] Okay, so here are the
steps for the job. Take a look.
The French noticed that
the bow end of the submarine
is completely flooded.
The two of you will go in
through the torpedo tubes
and then close 'em off.
Once you weld the hole shut,
you should be able
to open the door
to the interior.
W-Welding?
What do we do to get out?
Just make a hole in the
sub's hull and swim out.
Once we get what
we want out of there,
who cares what happens to it?
All right then,
let's get this over with.
I've never even done
weekend carpentry.
And we're supposed to do
all of this underwater?
I just don't see
how it'll work.
[REVY] Hey, are you done
checking the equipment?
If you keep up this bitching,
I'm gonna toss you overboard
without your tank.
Hm, yeah, I'm mostly done.
What about the
buoyancy compensator?
Did you test the
gauge? If you drown,
I'll leave you down there
in that metal casket
with those dead Nazis.
There's no need
to be difficult.
I said I'll be just fine.
If you die, you'll end up
causing me a lot of trouble.
So, stop talking back,
--you dumbass.
--[DUTCH] Revy, once you dive,
I'll only be able to
track you with the beacon.
Be careful not to
use up the batteries.
--Got it.
--[DUTCH] I almost forgot--
a little souvenir Balalaika
brought back from her homeland.
An underwater rifle! Does this
thing have full auto on it?
[DUTCH] Of course. Take it
as a good luck charm.
Okay, Rock. We better get going.
Just follow my lead!
So, you won her over with
a gun and saved Rock's ass.
You got a lot of
tricks up your sleeve.
Guess so. As an employer,
I worry about human relations.
All part of the job.
The beacon's been activated
and the PLRS is
working fine right now.
[DUTCH] Alright.
[BENNY] They're headed
straight for the salvage site.
Seems like Revy's used
to this kind of thing.
Of course she is.
I never would have hired her
if using those guns
was her only skill.
When it comes to swimming,
she's got natural talent.
Hmm...
--Uh, Dutch...
--What's up?
Come up here for a sec.
There's a ship.
[DUTCH] What?
We're not on a sea route.
The telecom company's
the only one who'd be here.
Telecom company?
I don't think so.
I've been listening
to their communications
ever since we got the offer.
They're not supposed to be out
here for another three days.
And besides,
that's a research ship.
And they seem to be carrying
some large equipment
on the back.
This isn't cool. You better
go raise our Thai Navy flag.
[BENNY] I'm on it.
[radio static]
[SOLDIER] To the vessel
currently idling in our path--
this is White Heather.
Please respond.
Well, well.
This is PT377 of the Thai Navy.
We are currently
on a mission here.
We'd like to inquire about your
purpose for being in this area.
Tell us your nationality,
ship number, and signal code.
[SOLDIER] We see
that you are acting
independently at
the present time.
Where is your mother ship?
That is classified
military information.
I'm requesting
for the second time
that you identify
yourself. Over.
[radio static]
These guys are
way too demanding.
Definitely not normal.
I'm going back
to the control room.
Keep track of them
and keep me posted.
We got some unusual cloud
activity. Fold up your parasol.
No problem. What do we
do about those two?
If their beacon's on,
we can find them anytime.
Worst case scenario,
we blast those guys
and then pick them up.
Hail Überführer!
Based on a communications
check using radio interception,
we confirm there are no
naval vessels in the vicinity.
Therefore, we can only conclude
that these are hated bandits
who are plundering
this sacred gravesite.
Your decision please, Commander.
These plunderers
are such fools.
The proof of inheritance
of this gravesite
is rightfully and
indisputably ours.
Very well, Squad Commander.
I will allow destruction
with an iron fist.
[BENNY] Hmm, what's going on?
Dutch. I'm seeing movement.
Okay. I'm just
starting the engines.
That's strange.
What are they doing?
Dutch, it's a TOW!
Damn it! I shoulda known
that's what they'd do!
Hang on, Benny!
Damn it! Fucking
anti-tank missiles!
That's it. Run away,
degenerationists.
For this is our destined
reunion with Brunhilda!
No one will stop us!
[ROCK] This underwater tomb
is about to open.
[REVY] You'll no longer
be one of us.
When that happens,
I'm gonna kill you.