[STANFORD]
So, this is Brunhilda.
It's a lot smaller
than I expected it to be.
[RACHMANN] It has an air to it
befitting of its grand ancestry.
And what an impressive
array of colors.
The piece is simply splendid.
Commander?
What is it?
Well, sir, although it may
be a valuable inheritance,
to use so many of our resources
for its retrieval
seems a bit...
It was Lord Alfred's
passion and grand vision
that we make this painting
the ideological basis
for our national
socialist movement.
This painting will bring
new life to our cause.
Try to understand.
--Sir!
--When we deliver this to him,
he has promised our party
considerable financial
assistance,
as well as an introduction
to the Anti-Communist Union.
Although our numbers are
small in America at present,
this is the opportunity we've
needed in order for our party
to make a significant
breakthrough.
[DUTCH] What is it
with that painting?
I mean, there's not much
we can do if these guys
have bad taste in politics
and even worse taste in art.
But still, coming all
the way out here
with that kind of
equipment and weaponry
is not something you can
do without a lot of money.
The investment is way out of
proportion to their objectives.
Or... wait a minute...
Talk about spending too
much money for the job.
So, that's it.
[DUTCH] You're pretty smart,
Rock. Sounds familiar, huh?
We've been hired to
find that same painting
and we're getting
a lot of cash to do it.
You'd think it was valuable.
But we're talking
about an artist
who was virtually unknown.
Well, hopefully that mystery's
gonna get solved tonight.
I have a bad feeling
about this.
[DUTCH] Rock, go and
feed Revy, will you?
Sure.
[DUTCH] Tell her they don't
deliver pizza out here.
So, she'll have to give up
and eat something from a can.
[ROCK] Revy.
I brought dinner.
Dutch says you should probably
have something to eat.
I'll leave it here.
If this is about what happened
earlier in the U-boat, I--
[REVY] Rock, we're done
talking about that.
I don't think
there's any reason
for us to go over all
that again. Got it?
Right.
[DUTCH] It's a good night.
The moon is about to sink,
then it'll get dark.
And when that happens,
we'll raid those bastards.
I've been keeping an eye
on the course of their ship
at the outer range
of our radar.
Good work. Revy and I
will take care of the rest.
Since they have
their little painting,
I'm guessing they're busy
celebrating right about now.
Idiots. That's right. Go ahead
and keep toasting each other.
We're gonna come in
banging on our tom-toms
and raid you like
the wild Apaches.
Wagner's shit next to that.
[classical music in distance]
Sorry, but we got one more
errand to run, partner.
[REVY] Sure. Why not?
[DUTCH] Your chance
to take those 92s
to these motherfuckers.
You distract 'em and
I'll do the searching.
We'll start some shit.
Works for me. I got no
complaints as long as I can
kill who I want and
steal what I want.
I'm going now, Rock.
You seem down, Revy.
What's going on? Did
something happen with Rock?
[REVY] Nothing happened.
[men laughing]
[Wagner's "Ride of the
Valkyries" plays]
Hmm?
I-I think we got trouble!
Someone--
And just like that, the first
little piggy met his end.
Oink, oink, oink.
[gunshots]
It's started.
I'm makin' my way to the
upper deck from the bow.
I need you to turn this place
into a cluster fuck. Okay?
Yeah. You don't
need to ask twice.
I'll eat till I get my fill.
What the hell? Where did
that gunshot come from?
I don't know.
[gunshots]
It's fine if they
wanna get wild,
but tell 'em to stop shooting.
Yes, sir.
[gunshots]
Commander! It's the enemy!
The enemy got on board!
We're under attack!
[alarm]
They're still at it.
[ROCK] Hey...
Times like this,
what are we supposed to
do while we're waiting?
Do we sit here smoking,
drinking beer, looking bored?
When you two were being
shot at earlier today,
I noticed Dutch remained
incredibly calm.
And to be honest,
I envied him for that.
But hey, we're not really
the type of people
who can pull out a gun and
shoot other human beings.
Let's face it, that's
why we watch the fort.
All squad leaders, gather your
men in front of the galley.
Remain there--
--Yo.
--Bastard. Shoot him!
What a joke! They've got the
uniforms, but that's about it.
So, is this where
the boss is hiding?
Y-You won't find the commander
here. He's on an upper level.
I swear it's the truth.
Well, thanks a lot.
That's very kind of you.
Revy, you hear me?
Revy? Revy? Where are you?
Damn it, that bitch!
Wait, please don't shoot.
All the sailors here
are hired outsiders.
We're not with these guys.
So what? "Please don't kill me"?
Unaffiliated and nonresistant
means nothing to me.
If you're all insured,
it shouldn't matter, right?
Oink, oink, oink.
Revy, what the hell
are you thinking?
Stanford. Eradicate these
hoodlums with a decisive blow.
Roger that.
What the hell's your problem?
I was just doing my job, Dutchy.
Bloodbaths are what we do
best. Isn't that right?
A gunman is a professional.
A shooter's someone who kills
'cause they got issues.
I do not remember hiring
Charles fucking Whitman.
If you want, you can go
wild and lose your shit.
But if you fuck this up
here and now, I die too.
Just keep your cool, Revy.
If that's too much for you,
go climb a fucking clock tower
and start shooting
up college kids.
Fuckin' great! So, now you're
gonna preach to me, too?
Spare me the bullshit, Dutch.
What do you expect, Two Hands?
I'm your employer, after all.
Huh, I actually thought
you were gonna kill me.
Me too, partner.
Not a whole lot of trust
going around here.
You couldn't even take
a joke. That's too bad.
So, why don't you tell me
what's next on the agenda,
big boss man.
The commander.
We're gonna find him.
[RACHMANN] Your Excellency,
the enemy is most likely those
grave robbers we spoke of.
Currently, our comrades are
boldly countering their attack
and dealing with them.
We'll be sure to get them.
So, please do not
worry, Your Excellency.
[ALFRED] Rachmann, not once has
a military unit been victorious
when entering a battle
with nothing more
than desired outcomes.
To say "please don't worry"
shows a lack of sincerity.
Would you not agree?
Unless you have some basis
for this confidence,
I would think it
best to refrain
from making such
casual consolations.
I-I'm sorry to
have offended you.
[ALFRED] Did I sound like I
wanted an apology from you?
Frankly, I'm quite surprised.
Do you think I'd place greater
importance on your apology
than the painting itself?
We spoke about this
at great length.
I want the painting
delivered to me
and you're in need of
connections into our world.
And that's about all there
is to it. Isn't that right?
You must understand that.
[DUTCH] Revy, have you
cooled off a bit?
[REVY] What do you mean?
Well, in case you
haven't noticed,
you get Whitman fever every time
we get a newcomer on board.
The exact same thing happened
when we took in Benny.
[REVY] Not digging too deep
is our style, isn't it?
I'll finish the job. Perfectly.
Of course you will.
Or you won't be able to
support your way of life.
I'm gonna check this area.
We'll finish talking later.
[wood breaking]
So, you're still
alive, little girl.
I complement you on
your audaciousness.
The name I've proudly carried
since birth is Blitz Stanford.
I am the acting captain of the
glorious Aryan Socialist Union.
And you, a nefarious
grave robber.
This is clearly the most
fated of confrontations.
For the sake of those
who died for the Union,
you shall atone
with your blood.
Behold!
Witness this mighty gun I wield.
I call it the Eiserne
Reich Luger Special.
The barrel is the
Luger artillery long
and the frame is
hardened carbon.
Featuring a thick grip
and a two-bullet chamber,
it is truly one of a kind.
This weapon is
far too destructive
to simply be referred to as
specialized in man-stopping.
I am the only one on Earth
capable of taming
this terrible gun!
Are you afraid?
There's no way you're not.
Now witness the
awesome power of--
[REVY] Shut the fuck up.
Didn't you see I
wasn't even listening?
I mean, were you trying to
sell me the damn gun or what?
You fucking coward--
Now it's my turn to talk.
Here's some advice--
if you can hit your target,
pretty much any gun
will do the trick.
Now that's one to grow on.
Say "hi" to the Führer
for me, would ya?
[gunshot]
[ALFRED] That's the
sound of the finale.
It appears that you've
lost the battle, Rachmann.
I've heard that tune
many times in the past.
Even now, I have fond
memories of those times.
Yo, Nazi.
I've come to get you.
Were you on the phone?
Well, after all
we've been through,
I don't think I'll apologize
for the rudeness.
Don't mind me. I'll wait
here and let you finish up.
[ALFRED] He certainly is a brave
man. I want to talk to him.
Put him on, will you?
It's for you.
[DUTCH] You the boss?
You're subordinates were a
real waste of good uniforms.
[ALFRED] Indeed.
You must forgive me for
the shameful display.
[DUTCH] Now I've got
two questions for you.
[ALFRED] Oh? About the
importance of the painting?
Let's start with that.
There's another
artist besides Janke
thought to be responsible
for this painting.
[ALFRED] I commend you
on your research.
[DUTCH] A little-known
artist from Austria.
Good old Adolf Hitler himself.
Or that's how the
rumor has it, anyway.
It's the Führer's?
[DUTCH] Don't rush to
conclusions, old man.
[ALFRED] The Führer
as an artist could,
at best, only paint
mediocre scenic pieces.
But the theory
brings back memories.
On the day he left for Batavia,
the SS officer carrying
that painting was also
under the impression that
it was the Führer's work.
[DUTCH] I see. So...
...what you want
isn't the painting,
but something else
inside of it.
And this is just
a wild guess, but
I'd be willing to bet
you know the phone number
to our office pretty well,
don't you, old man?
The antique trading
company from Madrid
that asked for
this salvage job.
Indeed, I'll admit that was me.
I was also the one who
wished you and Rachmann
to confront one another.
[RACHMANN]
What?
[ALFRED]
A most amusing method,
which provided insurance and
acted as their rite of passage.
And it's nothing more
than a fleeting
and dear memory to me now.
The day Heydrich decided
on the "Final Solution,"
we made a vow at
the Wannsee lakeside.
We would become realistic
guardians rather than idealists,
believing only in victory.
So, we gathered all of our
capital and created a file
which included our signatures
and account numbers.
When signs that
the end approached,
we hid our files
in four paintings
and escaped Berlin before
the Allies took the city.
That painting you have
there is the last piece.
You have shown surprising
insight, schwarzen.
You watch your mouth, you old
cracker. No need to be rude.
I might get upset and throw
it back into the ocean.
[ALFRED] That's fine with me.
I simply wanted to get it back
because it was discovered.
Financially speaking, we are
quite successful these days.
But what about the loss
of reputation for yourself?
Well, I don't like it, but I'm
not gonna argue with you there.
[ALFRED] You're a wise man.
You know, it's a real
shame you're black.
[DUTCH] I'll take that as
a complement. Now go on.
Continue with
your conversation.
[ALFRED] There won't
be any need for that.
He has already fulfilled
his role in all of this.
Alfred, you bastard!
First, you set me up
in this fixed race
and then you betray me?!
I suggest you watch
your mouth, young one.
Whether or not you
choose to admit it,
you and the black man were
given a level playing field.
You should have known
better than to try and
enter into our society
considering your ineptness.
I'm afraid you've only
yourself to blame.
As for you, black man,
that was a splendid job.
If you were fortunate enough
to have been born an Aryan,
I would have sent
you an Iron Cross.
I don't want one. All I want's
the money, you old Nazi fuck.
[ALFRED] Honesty is wonderful.
Hypocrisy rots this world.
I sincerely wish your kind
will one day be wiped off
the face of this planet.
[DUTCH] Thank you kindly.
And I sincerely wish
that you rot in hell.
Come on.
Are you still not
done cleaning up?
So, is this guy here
the commander?
[DUTCH] Yeah.
[REVY] Wanna make a bet, Dutch?
You know, the usual?
It's really not much
of a bet, Revy.
Let's just try it.
Here you go, old man.
Knock yourself out.
I say black.
I already told you,
it's not that much of a game.
I say black, too.
[whimpering]
Ahh!
I told you--it's not
that much of a bet.
You know, I thought the
commander might surprise us
and actually show some balls.
But I guess I was wrong.
These guys are all the same,
pathetic till the end.
[DUTCH] You're right about that.
Let's finish this job.
Fuckin' eh.
I sure got the shivers
today. Way too much trouble.
Shut up.
I won't cause any more trouble.
[DUTCH] I think I'm finally
starting to understand
what you're so hung up on.
And I'll tell you right now,
whatever's eating you
comes from deep inside.
In other words,
no amount of killing is gonna
make that pain disappear.
[REVY] Dutch?
[DUTCH] What is it?
It's Rock. He's on the
other side of the tracks.
He's nothing like
the people on our side.
I don't know why, but I just
can't stand that feeling.
It's not that I don't like him.
But, Dutch, it's just... It's
not possible. I just can't...
I can't partner with that guy.
Shut up! Shut the
fuck up, damn it!
I'm serious! I'll kill you!
[ROCK] Fine. Then do it.