[FUJIWARA] I imagine it's
probably daybreak there soon.
The sea at daybreak.
Spare me the sentiment.
Only worthless students and
the permanently unemployed
find that sort of
thing appealing.
[FUJIWARA] Uh...
However, I agree these
winter skies are depressing.
At this point, we know that
Okajima is in the Sea of Heaven.
I'm going to need you to
book us a flight down there
--right away.
--Uh, sure.
A business trip, Sir?
Why don't we go down there,
as well? To the Sea of Heaven.
[birds chirping]
Damn it. Will someone tell me
why I have to suffer like this?!
Rock! What the hell
are you thinking?
Do you have any idea how much
one of those things costs?
This is it. They came
here to kill me.
Why should I have to
suffer for all this crap
my boss got us involved in?
I think you're missing
the point here.
What they really want is to
destroy that disc, right?
Your life is just--
My life is just an
accessory to that.
--Damn it. Damn it! Damn it!
--Uh...
You know there's
a torpedo in there.
[ROCK] Shut up. Shut up!
Hey, Benny, doesn't this
seem kind of weird to you?
[BENNY] Yeah,
something's not right.
They've stopped
firing completely.
They could have easily made
us into Swiss cheese by now.
No doubt. Something's
wrong here.
Dutch, what the hell's goin' on?
--Where'd those guys go?
--Benny-boy?
[BENNY] Yeah.
It looks like they've fallen
back about 5,000 meters
and they're still tailing
us from that distance.
What do these guys want, anyway?
Yeah, what is it?
[DUTCH] Damn it. The channel.
[BENNY] That's it! The channel.
The path ahead of us to
Belawan is filled with rocks
and mangroves and they
must have figured that out.
The further we go, the
tighter it's gonna get.
In the end, we won't be able
to take evasive maneuvers.
Let's turn this boat around
and get out of here.
Yeah.
[helicopter]
You better not say
I suck at this.
But I guess I can't
redeem myself now, right?
I wouldn't say that.
[DUTCH] I didn't have
any other options.
I had to evade to the right.
Yeah, I know that.
Did we just enter
the mouth of a river?
This is a river, right?
If we continue like this,
we're going to run out
of options to escape.
[REVY] Yeah, we already
figured that one out.
These guys have us
completely trapped.
The enemy's behind us again.
He's looking down on us
from about 5,000 meters
back right now.
[REVY] Check that out.
A sunken ship.
What a bad omen.
[EO CAPTAIN] This is fine.
We'll wait right here.
Go on. Off you go.
You want to show me your
little assets, fine with me.
But we both know that you'll be
coming back to me real soon.
And when you do, we're
going to go head-to-head.
Hurry back. I'll be waiting.
Then we can put an end to this.
Dutch, they just stopped
by that sunken ship
and they're hovering there.
They're not chasing us anymore.
Huh. It's not worth the
energy for them to follow us.
That's exactly what this means.
Damn.
It's a dead end.
Sure is.
Damn it!
[EO CAPTAIN] Hey, Mayer.
[MAYER] Sir?
[EO CAPTAIN] I'm gettin' real
hard right now just imagining
how they're going to react
to a situation like this.
[MAYER] I'd say they have
zero chance of beating us.
Given our superior weaponry,
I'm sure we'll honeycomb
that boat of theirs.
That's exactly why I can't wait
to see how they're gonna react.
If they make this boring for
us and don't even fight back,
then we'll be sure to
kill them nice and slow.
There's no road ahead of us.
The only option we have
now is to turn around.
And when we do that,
they'll be waiting for us.
My gut tells me he
put us here on purpose.
They want to finish
us off face-to-face.
So, who wants to ring the gong?
Humph.
It ain't something
that happens every day,
but once in a while,
you find them around.
Wannabe vets who like to
pretend they're cowboys.
Wait a second. You're saying
our only choice is to die?
[DUTCH] Alright, why don't
you calm down, Rock?
[ROCK] I know, let's call
the local police.
I mean, that's got
to be better than--
[grunting]
You're not helping. Now
like I said, just calm down.
Panicking isn't going
to solve anything.
If you want to survive, you
need to start using your head.
Dutch, how 'bout waiting
for them to run out of fuel?
Yeah, but these
bastards are from EO.
They'll come finish the
job before that happens.
[ROCK] Damn it.
Why did things have
to end up like this?
Not this one. I'd like
a business paper.
I have to check on my stocks.
Certainly. Right away,
Mr. Kageyama.
How bad's the ship?
[DUTCH] So far,
she's not looking too bad,
but I'm more worried
about those things.
If even a single bullet
hits a torpedo,
we'll all be
flying to the moon.
That's what you get for
keeping them, dumbass.
[DUTCH] Hmm.
I always figured I'd end up
using them for something.
I know it's a waste, but maybe
we should throw those overboard.
[DUTCH] Guess we have no choice.
[REVY] What a waste.
[ROCK] Wait. Dutch,
listen to me.
[DUTCH] You go back to sleep.
I've figured something out,
now that I've had time to think.
Just hear me out.
If you break my
concentration again,
then I'll let Revy
hit you next time.
And it ain't gonna be pretty.
I say we go face-to-face
with these guys.
[DUTCH] Are you retarded?
How can we have a shootout?
All we have on board
is an anti-tank rifle.
They've got missiles
on their side.
I noticed that chopper had
infrared homing missiles on it,
actually.
[DUTCH] We don't
even come close.
You think so? We do have
something we can use.
[DUTCH] Revy, what have you
been giving him to drink?
[REVY] Don't blame me for this.
If you think about it,
this is just a big
game of chicken, right?
This boat's armaments and speed,
that sunken ship we passed...
I'm pretty sure we have
everything we need.
What the hell do you
have in mind, anyway?
[ROCK] Exactly what you guys
were just talking about.
Why don't we fly them
to the moon instead?
Impossible. There's no way
we can pull that off.
If you think about it,
in theory, this ship is
designed to hydroplane.
At full speed, we're only
in the water this much.
Well, Dutch, it's not like
we've got any better options.
I say we do it.
You do realize that
the plan's not gonna work
unless they're
right in front of us.
Do you really think
that's gonna happen, Rock?
It seems like they're having
a lot of fun chasing us around,
even though it's obvious
they have the advantage.
What reason would they have
to start the whole
fight over again?
You said it earlier, yourself--
this is the type of guy
who thinks of himself
as a real cowboy.
If we lure him into
a game of chicken,
he won't be able to resist.
I don't have any guarantees.
At this point, it's your
decision to make as Captain.
[DUTCH] We sure managed
to pick ourselves up
one crazy son of a bitch.
You've got to be
completely insane...
...but the idea's exciting.
And what's the point of life
if you can't get excited?
Right. Let's do this thing!
[MAYER] The radar's picked up
something, Captain.
Our target's on the move.
I accept your challenge.
[DUTCH] Rock, you know what
you've got to do, right?
If they fire a missile,
I shoot the signal flare
away from the boat.
You got it.
I see the jackass. Revy!
It's a game of chicken.
Send 'em an invitation.
[MAYER] They're firing at us!
[EO CAPTAIN]
Of course they are.
About time, too, so let's play.
Rock, they're coming.
Shoot that flare!
[beeping]
[ROCK] It worked.
[BENNY] We're on
the alpine course now.
Both of you get
back in the cabin.
[EO CAPTAIN] They want to use
that old wreck as a shield?
It won't do much good.
Hey, Mayer!
--Yes, Sir.
--Once they're clear,
we'll nail 'em
with a single shot.
We're gonna put an end to
this duel once and for all.
You're about to
get fucked, baby.
[BENNY] Three hundred
feet to go.
One fifty.
One hundred!
Fire number one!
Fire number two!
[ROCK] Yeah! You got fucked!
[birds chirping]
Well, feels like my
head's still attached.
My sunglasses aren't broken.
Amen, hallelujah,
and peanut butter.
Fucking hell.
We made it this time,
but I will never do this again.
[DUTCH] Benny, you okay?
[BENNY] Yeah,
I'm alive... somehow,
but all my instruments
are fucked.
We're gonna have to
fix all this up or--
--Wait a minute. Hold up.
--[BENNY] Oh, man...
What about Rock?
He's passed out over there.
He was yelling like a maniac
right before we hit 'em.
Just like William Holden
in The Wild Bunch.
[DUTCH] Just look at him.
He looks so comfortable
sprawled out like that.
Yeah, no kidding.
[ROCK] And just like that,
the moment passed.
All the excitement I'd
felt from the adrenaline
just disappeared somewhere.
And my boiling blood
had returned to normal.
Where am I? And what
am I doing here?
[BALALAIKA] Excellent work.
You know, I really admire
smart work, Dutch.
But I've got to tell you,
you guys are all
looking a little rough.
Well, it's not like we're
going to some dinner party.
It's just our style.
Now, Mr. Kageyama,
we from Hotel Moscow
have a code of honor.
Oh? I thought you
were a representative
of the Bougainvillea
Trade Company.
[BALALAIKA] As you can see,
we followed through on
our end of the bargain.
So, there shouldn't
be any hard feelings.
Of course not.
The world is full of things
that cannot be helped.
[BALALAIKA] Now it's your turn
to follow through on
your end of the bargain.
We'll go over the
details at the hotel.
[KAGEYAMA] Very well then.
Thanks for your good
work on this, Okajima.
Now come along. Let's go.
Well, Okajima, what are you
waiting for? Come on.
[ROCK] Hey, Boss.
Don't you remember?
Well, you should.
I'm already dead.
You said it, remember?
And by the way,
my name is Rock now.
That so? Very well.
Do as you wish.
Let's get going, Fujiwara.
[FUJIWARA] Y-Yes, Sir.
Well, Rock,
I owe you an apology for making
you talk to those idiots.
And yet, it would have been a
waste for a tough guy like you
to remain as a Japonski.
I want you to come to us if
there's anything you ever need.
Goodbye.
Okajima...
Okajima's no longer
an employee of ours.
The look in his eyes
is all the proof I need.
Yes, but what could have
changed in such a short time?
None of it matters anymore.
[DUTCH] So, tell me, Rock--
what will you do now?
Guess I'm not a hostage anymore
and I've got nowhere to go.
Hey, there's this
crew I've heard of
that might be looking for
a good sailor. You think you
could be interested
in something like that?
They're a delivery company.
Who sometimes break the rules
to put food on the table.
Isn't that right?
[horn sounding]
What's wrong?
There appears to
be a small vessel
blocking our way, Captain.
We've been sounding the horn
for a while, but it won't budge.
What is that thing?
Well, it was inevitable
that some information
would be leaked,
and I think we were all
prepared for that to happen.
It was a job well done,
Kageyama.
Thank you very much,
Sir. I am honored.
[classical music]
[ROCK] Uhh... Testing,
testing. Um...
Good morning to everybody who's
presently aboard the St. Joan.
[REVY] Why won't you
wear that Hawaiian shirt
I got for you at the
market? It's a good fit.
Because we happen to be at work.
That's right, I consider
this to be my job now.
Um...To everybody
aboard the St. Joan--
I apologize for
the sudden request,
but I'm going to
have to ask you
to please stop your
ship right away.
[horn sounding]
My own personal opinion
is that at this point--
[metal clanking]
Complying with this request
as quickly as possible
would definitely be, uh,
the best course of action.
[BENNY] Dutch,
the St. Joan has opened up
communications with us.
We finally made contact.
And what did they say?
"Move aside immediately
or we'll have no choice
but to force our way through."
Well, I guess it can't
be helped. Okay, Benny.
--Revy.
--Good.
I was sick of waiting.
[DUTCH] Looks like playtime
is officially over.
Okay.
Everyone, please take cover.
It's times like this that
bring out the savage in me.
Jesus!
My god! They must have a rocket
launcher on board, Captain.
Hand that over!
[ROCK] Wait.
Listen very carefully,
you dipshits--
my rockets are much faster
than any of your
lame distress signals.
Unless you want to end up
as a corpse-filled shipwreck,
then I suggest you
stop moving. You got it?!
[classical music]
Okay, Benny-boy, give notice
to Lyun E. Pan's guys
that we've taken the St. Joan.
And you tell them that they'd
better come pick her up
before anyone starts
a ruckus out here.
Roger that.
[KAGEYAMA] I'm home.
Hey, John. There's a good boy.
[toilet flushing]
[KAGEYAMA]
Takanori, how are things?
Huh?
[KAGEYAMA] Your studies
for the entrance exams?
Not so good.
Oh, what a surprise.
You're home today.
Mm-hmm.
We need to talk
about your daughter.
She's been getting home
later and later these days.
She's still only an
18-year-old girl, you know.
Could you say something to her?
[KAGEYAMA] I thought that
was your responsibility.
Hmm... the stocks.
Hey, Daddy, what color was the
sea in that really warm country
where you just went to?
That one for your business trip?
[KAGEYAMA] Color of the sea?
I don't really know.
Daddy was busy working
the whole time down there.
[ROCK] There's probably no one
who'd believe me, but...
...I've become a pirate
of the South Seas.
That huge ship
was today's catch.
[REVY] Okay, we need to get
back to port before lunch.
The china bowl at Kao Han...
...always sells out quickly.
[ROCK] We're actually
being targeted by pirates?
Dutch! What's the
background on our client?