Hey! Someone slashed my tires!
Who the hell would do this?
It'd better not be scratched...
[siren]
No, there's nothing.
As far as I can tell,
they were never here.
By the way, who tipped you off
that this place was
being used as a hideout?
Huh? You got it by fax?
Ogami?! Fuck!
Ogami's under attack!
I want you down there
right now! And make it fast!
What the hell do you want?
I said leave the
deliveries for later!
[explosion]
Tch! Boss, I can't get a hold
of the Sagamihara office.
And I haven't had any word
from Taguchi since last night.
I'm afraid they're all dead.
Taguchi and his team.
Who told you?
The police found them
at the Bokuto lumber yard.
Their bodies, that is.
They've asked me to
come down to the station
for questioning tomorrow.
It seems I can be held
responsible as an employer
under the Anti-Organized
Crime laws.
I understand now. They don't
fight like the mafia.
The way they operate...
they're like an army.
That's why they call her
Kapitän . I should've known.
[BORIS] We're in the final
stages of destroying
all Washimine locations.
[POLANSKI] Bases 371 and 2
have been wiped out.
Daniel's team is currently
en route to base 221.
They'll commence at 1505.
Has Corporal Razal
met his objective yet?
[BORIS] They're
tied up in traffic
on the highway at the moment,
but they will meet the deadline.
[phone ringing]
Yellow Delta 23.
This is Corporal Jodorowsky.
Report.
[JODOROWSKY] Everything's
gone according to plan.
We'll now be withdrawing
from the operation zone.
[BORIS] Roger. Return to base.
215's under our control.
[BALALAIKA] It's looking good.
The death of
Officer Shigeru Ito
has been confirmed
at location 317.
[BALALAIKA] Alright.
Excellent work, comrades.
In only three more moves,
the princess will fall.
I got a hold of Balalaika.
Looks like we're off duty.
She says she'll have another
job for us sometime tomorrow.
--[ROCK] Yeah.
--What's wrong? You look gloomy.
I'm not quite sure.
[REVY chuckling]
[ROCK] But look at you. You seem
to be having a good time.
You can see right through me,
can't ya, Rock?
I guess we've been working
together too long.
Running into a guy like Jumbo
makes me grateful
I chose this career.
I mean, you think
you've seen it all
and then some crazy-ass
samurai slices a bullet in half
right in front of you.
Fuckin' incredible.
I can't wait till
I get my chance.
Why don't you just
kill yourself?
Wouldn't that be easier?
[REVY] Kill myself, huh?
I'm sorry, but you're
missing the point, Rock.
We already are the walking
dead. Don't you know that?
Dutch, Balalaika, Chang, and
all the other people we know...
Every single one of us who's
running around Roanapur is dead.
There's one difference between
us and the real dead...
[ROCK] Difference?
Yeah. Unlike most people,
whether we live or die
isn't a big deal for us.
Besides, if you cling to life,
you live in fear of death
and that fear will
cloud your judgment.
But once you've managed
to free yourself of that,
you can go on fighting
to the end of the world.
[ROCK] Oh, I see.
So, given the choice,
you prefer to die
in the gutter then?
Somehow, Roanapur
seems so far away...
Hey, Rock! What's your problem?
You're being a real bitch today,
in case you haven't noticed.
I know. I'm sorry. The booze is
bringing out the worst in me.
Ahh. It's no big deal.
Young lady, you
should be careful
when you're playing
games with adults.
You wanted the successor
to be a blood relative.
I'm only here because of
the conditions you set.
This has been
acknowledged by the Peace--
Don't fuck with us,
you little brat!
Shut up, Morozumi.
I don't plan on
allowing you to succeed.
But more importantly, you need
to tell me what you're gonna do
about these Russians
you imported.
I'll be the first to admit,
that was a big mistake.
The Washimine Clan is now doing
everything within its
power to expel our enemy.
[KOUSA] You're missing the
point, Washimine princess.
I'm asking how you
plan to repay us...
...for the many losses
that we've incurred.
With all due respect,
surely you remember the reason
why our last boss, Bando,
took this desperate measure.
Under the circumstances, his
options were quite limited.
[KOUSA] We're not responsible
for Bando's misplaced
resentment.
We were generous enough to
send you a replacement boss
to try and protect
our brother organization.
And who was it
that turned us down?
Very well then.
We shall let the Peacekeeping
Council settle this.
You little brat!
You're in way over your head
taking a stance
like that, goddamn it!
We know that the council has the
authority to direct mediation
and we've managed to build
enough of a case
for their consent.
You bitch!
Are we supposed to
be frightened by that?
[YUKIO] He wasn't the
slightest bit concerned...
It may be pointless to go
to the council with this.
But that's...
The people in this world
are consumed by greed.
Money is the only thing
they have any respect for.
Given that, it's
clear which side
would be more beneficial
for them to take.
So, honor and justice are dead.
[GINJI] It pains me to say so,
but I'm obliged to remind you...
In its present state,
the Washimine Clan
has been reduced to
one-third of its numbers
since the fighting began.
The Russians' attacks
have been devastating.
They made a point of
eliminating our leaders first,
which has only further
destabilized us.
They haven't eliminated us.
You and I are still here.
Mr. Inoue.
--Yes?
--Please pull over.
Sure, Boss.
But, Miss, wouldn't
that mean we'd be--
Yes. That's what it means.
Promise me you'll
send the message
to everyone who's still alive.
But, Miss, why?!
The remaining members
have been loyal...
...and I cannot afford
to lose any others.
You too, Mr. Inoue.
The two of us will create
an opportunity to strike.
Until then, please
stay alive and wait.
Now then, Miss...
I won't let things end
this way. That's a promise.
[GINJI] Every single
one of our offices
has surveillance cameras,
but they were aware of that.
It seems they've destroyed all
of them, including the tapes.
[YUKIO] Well, it's in pretty
bad shape, but I managed to
retrieve this piece of
videotape from the scene.
I was able to
sneak in and get it
before the police could
seal off the building.
Did you see that?
I sure did.
It looks like they're using
electric company vans.
If only we knew where
they were coming from.
This would be a lot easier
if we had access
to the N-system
that the police use.
Indeed.
[people screaming]
[alarm sounding]
[YUKIO] Wow, what a feeling!
That was thrilling!
I feel like we're Bonnie
and Clyde or something!
Works for me.
Pretty soon, we'll be
robbing banks in Bolivia!
[GINJI laughing]
[OFFICER 1 on radio] An armed
robbery has just occurred
at the credit union
on the fourth block of Inoue.
Two suspects, both considered
armed and dangerous.
They're escaping
in a white van
with a red spade mark
painted on the door.
All officers in the area
should be on the lookout
and ready to engage
them if necessary....
Mr. Okajima is
standing on the border
of two different worlds...
And somewhere between
those worlds exists a city
where only gangsters
and criminals dwell.
[GINJI] That sounds good
to me. To be a yakuza,
making a name for yourself
in a place like that.
The name of the
city is Roanapur.
They say Balalaika's
from there, as well.
You know, secretly,
I always wished
that our life in Takamachi
would somehow go on forever.
Me, too.
With all the musicians
and the shops...
We always had so much fun
together there.
But I think...
...this is even more fun.
Well, let's just focus
on one thing at a time.
We're gonna hafta deal with
this Russian lady first
if we wanna live in that city.
Still, this is getting exciting.
[OFFICER 2 on radio] This is
patrol car Shinagawa 142.
We just spotted a van
with a red spade mark
heading north
along the shoreline.
Suspect is refusing
to pull over.
--Requesting backup.
--We've got them, Ginji.
The shoreline...
close to Tokyo Port.
This is Jodorowsky.
[sirens]
We're being pursued
by a squad car.
[BORIS] Lose them.
[YUKIO] Balalaika. They came
from Roanapur. But how?
With all those weapons
and equipment,
they'd never get
through an airport.
Unless...
A ship! Balalaika
must be at the port!
He was able to lose them. We'll
have to get rid of the van.
But how? How did the police
manage to find out what
vehicles we're using?
I'd say it was the first
effective countermeasure
that girl's taken. I think
we're being challenged.
How amusing. We'll have to make
a point of crushing this one.
[YUKIO] Knowledge exists
so that we may forget reality.
But there are
things that create
a greater sense of escapism
than text can offer.
And there is a place
that embodies this...
Roanapur.
[gunfire and sirens in distance]
Oh, boy.
With Balalaika away, this
city's verging on total chaos.
So, you avoid getting shot?
Barely. This is just crazy.
The Triad's doing what they can,
but it's a mess out there.
A gun paradise.
Beneath the surface,
that's all this city really is
and everyone loves it.
Boss Chang knows that
better than anyone.
[BENNY] All I know is it's
a good thing Rock's not here.
Guns just aren't his thing.
You've got to realize
something about Rock, Benny.
The fact that he hasn't had
to hold a gun is a blessing.
[BENNY] Yeah, why is that?
'Cause if he shoots
the way he talks,
his bullets'll
ricochet back at us.
It'd be too damn dangerous.
[BENNY laughing]
[DUTCH]
You see me laughing? Shit.
Sorry to make you wait.
We haven't been here long.
So, what's our next job?
[BALALAIKA] It's another
meeting... with the Japanese.
And if this one goes well,
we'll be going home soon.
A meeting?
But the Washimine Clan isn't...
We'll be talking to...
the Kousa Clan.
This way, we take care of all
of our problems in one move.
Not bad, huh?
[YUKIO] Because the truth is...
...you don't actually
want to save me.
I remind you of the normal life
you thought you'd thrown away.
That's all.
[BALALAIKA] As long as
they're well behaved,
I suppose we might
consider agreeing
to at least one of
their conditions.
Hey. Hey, Rock!
Is this it?
Are you going to remain
in the twilight forever?
[ROCK] Miss Balalaika.
You have no reason to ally
with them at this point.
The Washimine Clan
is a waste of time.
You're better off
destroying the Kousa Clan.
--Dumbass!
--The Washimine Clan
has been considerably weakened.
So... that means they're
no longer a threat to you.
Am I right? Not to mention,
Washimine's--
Rock!
Don't misunderstand
your position.
You are here as my
interpreter. Nothing more.
You're not my fellow
soldier, my comrade,
or with Hotel Moscow,
understand?
[ROCK] Washimine's new leader
is a teenager!
Hey, hey! Cut it out!
Surely you must still have
some sense of justice!
Enough, Rock. I've had it!
[REVY] Damn it!
Let's all calm down.
Whaddya say, Sis?
We don't wanna reenact a scene
from My Bloody Valentine
here, do we?
Shut it, Revy.
Rock, look at me.
Justice?
I can't think of another word
more loved by the people.
It does have a nice ring to it.
However... without ever
exercising your own strength,
you seek the death of others
at the hands of someone else.
Well, the justice you refer
to smells pretty rotten to me.
The stench of a bloodbath.
Wouldn't you agree?
Don't give me that look, Rock.
After all, I'm not
upset with you.
--[REVY] Sis!
--Of all the people I know,
I just never thought I'd hear
those words coming from you.
I'm amused. That's all this is.
[REVY] Alright. You've made your
point, now just let him go.
My fingers are twitching.
In the grand scheme, our
lives are insignificant.
They're light as air,
much like a candy wrapper.
[REVY] I'm really not in
the mood to talk right now.
Just let him go.
And Two-Hands, I have
something to say to you.
I don't know what's going on
in that head of yours,
but it will only bring
you disappointment
if you hope to have
a life like his.
Shut up. I know. I know
what you're saying, okay?
So, please, just shut up now.
I'm warning you, I've just
about reached my limit.
Miss Balalaika. Your
victory here is assured
and you no longer have anything
to lose, so isn't that--
[REVY] Rock!
[ROCK]
Isn't that enough for you?!
Fuckin' idiot!
[BALALAIKA] No, it isn't enough.
There are two
things to remember
when you're begging
for your life.
One is to try and
entertain the person
holding the gun to your head.
And the other is to
give that person...
...a convincing reason why
they shouldn't kill you.
But you haven't managed to do
either one of those things.
So, let's hear it!
What obligation do you have
to save them, anyway?!
[ROCK] You're misunderstanding.
--Oh?
--It's not an obligation.
And it's got nothing
to do with justice.
The only reason I wanna do it
is because... it's my hobby.
Hobby?
Yeah, that's right.
Some people like to
die in the gutters,
others like to go to war.
Then there's me...
When it comes down to it,
I'm really no
different from you.
[BALALAIKA laughing]
Things are gonna pick up
again tomorrow, Rock.
Oh, and from here on,
I think you'd be wise
not to risk your life
on stupid games.
Park the car somewhere,
will you?
Thanks.
Rock! Fuckin' shit-for-brains!
The only fuckin' reason
we're not dead right now
is because for some
fuckin' reason,
that fuckin' war maniac bitch
put her gun away!
Or maybe it was God's grace
or your great sense of humor!
Yeah, I agreed to be your
gun while we were here,
but this is fucked!
I could protect you
through the fuckin' Alamo!
But it's just not fuckin'
possible to protect a guy
who's trying so damn hard to get
fuckin' killed all the time!
--Are you mad?
--Not even close!
I'm fuckin' pissed!
Anyone but you, this would
have been a bloodbath!
Revy.
Listen... I'm going back home...
...once more. I want
you to come with me.
[REVY] I don't need
Balalaika to tell me.
Your home is a good place.
I guess that's why
I got a little lost.
But it's so far away,
I could never reach it.
I've survived on dirty
air my entire life.
For a second there, I
think I even forgot that
I don't know how to live...
anywhere else.
In the end, it's just the sis.
All she ever thinks about
is starting a war.
Go ahead. Off you go
and don't look back.
You're about to wake up
from your nightmare.
[ROCK] Revy.
Have you forgotten?
I'm already dead.
I think I died
the day I met you.
If Roanapur is the city
of the walking dead,
then this is the
city of the living.
This place is
so familiar to me,
it was easy to forget
that, I suppose.
But to look at it now
through a dead man's eyes,
this place is a mirage.
No. This place
might've been a mirage
even back when I lived here,
but I just couldn't see it then.
Revy. I didn't come here
to go back to my old life.
I came here to forget.
I came here 'cause
I'd rather see through
whatever's gonna happen
than turn back.
You're gonna regret it, Rock.
I stopped regretting
a year ago.
I just didn't have
the resolve to let go.
But now I think...
I've got that, too.
I see.
Hey! Look, it's Calamity Jane!
Yeah, you're right.
Um, hey, could you maybe
show us that trick again?
Yeah, please!
Shoot the cans down!
Yeah! C'mon! Do it!
Well, Rock?
Put on a show for 'em, Revy.
[REVY] Alright.
What kind of...
...gun is that?
I-It looks real.
[REVY] This here's
a Beretta M92 Custom,
The Praiyachat Sword
Cutlass Special.
Now watch those cans
carefully, you little brats.
Yeah, this is gonna blow
your minds, alright?!
Your mommies are waiting for ya.
Now go on home, you brats!
[YUKIO] Ginji. I would like to
have a more powerful weapon.
--Miss...
--I'm fairly certain
we have one somewhere.
[GINJI] I'm not very familiar
with projectiles.
Apparently, this is a Russian
gun called a Stechkin.
I'm told the bullets are big
and it can keep firing
like a machine gun.
Though it may be too
much for you, Miss.
No. I'd like to be able to
pull my own weight from now on.
I like this one.
[BENNY] The good city
of Roanapur, huh...
...where the power of guns
meets the power of liquor.