[rain and thunder]
[GRETEL] I can't think
of his name, fratele meu .
Who was it that said "The
ultimate love is cannibalism"?
Edgar Allan Poe?
[HANSEL] I don't think so,
sora mea .
Wasn't he a necrophiliac?
[GRETEL] Richard Matheson?
[HANSEL] I couldn't
say for sure.
[GRETEL] I wonder if they were
ever treated to this scent.
[gun cocking]
[MAN 1 screaming and gasping]
[MAN 1]  Ahh!
[rapid gunfire]
[GRETEL] The smell of life
flowing out from the body.
[HANSEL] The scent
of rust and sea salt.
[GRETEL] The smell of
a man's last breath.
[HANSEL] It's true, we're
very fortunate, sora mea .
[GRETEL] I wonder
how long before
the people of this
city start to move.
[HANSEL] This is our eighth.
I guess we did kill a few
we didn't plan on killing.
Everyone will be coming
to try and kill us now.
I really can't wait,
sora mea .
[GRETEL] Yes, fratele meu .
[kissing sound]
[HANSEL sighing]
[GRETEL] I can't wait either.
[phone ringing]
[ROCK] Hello, Lagoon
Company. Oh, hi, Mr. Boris.
What? Okay, so the
meeting is cancelled?
[BORIS] Yeah. Sorry about that.
I'll call you within
the next few days.
We'll work something out.
[DUTCH] What's up, Rock?
Looks like the meeting's
been cancelled.
He didn't say why, but I guess
something must've come up.
[REVY] Dutch,
you think it's that?
Probably. And I'm pretty
sure that won't end well.
[ROCK] What are you
talking about?
What the fuck?
[REVY] You seriously haven't
heard anything about this?
No, I...
There's been a
bunch of murders.
Not to sound callous,
but homicides aren't
unusual in this city.
Yeah, I know murder isn't
exactly front-page news,
but when they're
targeting Hotel Moscow,
that's a different story.
Hmm? Hotel Moscow?
[REVY] They found five corpses,
all with ties to the Russians,
and that's just
in the last month.
Revy. That information's
out of date.
There's six now.
[REVY] Ugh...
In any case, it means
some asshole's trying to
pour gas on an open flame.
And you can be sure
that in this city,
where the balance of
power walks a tightrope
on its fucking hands,
we'll all be knee-deep
in blood before this ends.
[BALALAIKA] Another
one's been killed.
An accountant this time.
Are we in Beirut?
Mogadishu perhaps?
That's enough already.
[CHANG] Do I need to remind you
why we decided
to meet here today?
This is an era of coexistence.
And I'd like to preserve
this equilibrium we've managed
to reach through all
the bloodshed and bullets.
Miss Balalaika.
Is that so, Mr. Chang?
Maybe you can
refresh my memory.
When did I say
I wanted coexistence?
Hmph. Again with that
mouth of yours, huh?
A fuckin' peasant Ivan bitch
who thinks her shit don't stink.
Priceless. Go back to
digging your potatoes.
[BALALAIKA] Hmph.
Well, I guess we can't
all be Italian, right?
Which reminds me,
I've heard that guido guts
tend to smell like a pig's.
--Is that true?
--[VERROCCHIO] Fuckin' bitch!
[CHANG] Okay, I think
that's enough. Both of you.
Or have you forgotten
why we're all here?
All of us hold grudges
against each other
over one thing
or another, right?
However, it's also in all
of our own best interests
to cooperate at this time.
If you've got business to
discuss, then I'm all ears.
But you can feed your
personal honor to the dogs.
That's just something you
accept in our line of work.
Miss Balalaika,
this may be news to you,
but some of my men
were hit, as well.
Hmm...
[CHANG] A member of the 14K and
a directly affiliated executive
in a whorehouse
on Rachiada Street.
They were killed the
same way yours were.
What's going on, Chang?
Someone here's trying to
shift the balance of power!
Abrego! Look at me!
Hey, what the fuck?!
I had nothing to
do with this shit!
You and me, we had some
issues between us in the past,
but I thought we
worked all that out!
Okay, fine then.
So, do us all a favor and
ask Verrocchio who did this.
That's bullshit and
you know it, Fry Face!
As it happens, we lost one
of our recruiters, as well.
So, what does that
make, nine bodies?
Listen--no one from this city
would pull
something like this.
It's probably some drifter.
Someone who doesn't know
how things work around here.
Alright, if we can
agree that these killings
are the work
of some outsider,
we can start
working together
to hunt down
whoever's responsible.
Also, we'll make
a declaration.
We don't need our people
killing each other out there.
Any objections?
I don't like this.
It's a goddamned farce.
Psh. Shut the fuck up!
Balalaika, I wouldn't
be so hasty if I were you.
I doubt it's in
your best interest
to rip this entire city apart.
Ugh. Is this a social
gathering, Mr. Chang?
Are we going to be playing
a hand of gin rummy next?
Let me be absolutely
clear about this--
the reason we came here today
was to make our position known.
Hotel Moscow will
not tolerate people
who obstruct our operations.
Whoever dares to will
be destroyed. Denounced.
Then we'll kill his family,
his friends, even the pet dog,
if we feel it's necessary.
That went well.
Look. Everyone in here is
carrying a gun of some kind.
It's like we're in
a parallel universe
where everyone's Clint Eastwood.
[REVY] Why wouldn't they be?
Right now there's a fucking
head case out there,
who thinks he's
some kinda punisher.
[ROCK] Punisher...
One who gives punishment...
But punishment
for what exactly?
[REVY] Who knows?
These days, Roanapur
is like popcorn.
It's just simmering
on heat right now,
ready to pop at any minute.
[distant thunder]
[BAO] Have you heard, Revy?
Apparently, there's a bounty.
How much?
[BAO] Fifty grand. And that's
not Thai baht, either.
It's in US dollars.
Fuck. They're really
serious about this, huh?
What are we waiting for?
[BAO] Well, do you
have any leads?
No. But if it's an outsider,
they shouldn't be
that hard to find.
It's true. An outsider
would be easy to spot.
The city's not
that big, after all.
At least that was the
case with the Lovelace maid.
But no one seems to have a
clue where this outsider is,
which means someone's
providing a hideout.
We just don't
know who it is yet.
And that's what's
got everyone on edge.
Well, I don't give
a rat's ass what happens
as long as my place
don't get shot up again.
[REVY] You worry too much, Bao.
You know this is
a neutral district.
No one's gonna
start anything here.
Well, if it isn't Two Hands.
--Huh?
--My,
you're drinking the cheap
shit again, are you?!
Business ain't so good lately?
[REVY] Eda! What the fuck?!
[ROCK] Who's she?
Th-That sister from
the Ripoff Church!
Well, well, I see you
brought Romeo with you.
Hi there. How you been?
Why don't you
ditch this wild boar
and come drink with
a real woman, baby?
I know your night's
not complete
till you're getting
banged by a stranger,
but fuck off!
Ooh. Scary.
Hear that, Romeo?
You never know when
she's on the rag.
She's pretty irregular.
You asked for it, bitch!
Let's step outside! You and me!
Don't get your panties
in a twist, Two Hands.
I didn't come here to
pick a fight with you.
I've got a story that
might interest you.
One that might be
worth some money.
You're talking about
this bounty, right?
You heard?
Actually, Revy and I were
just talking about that.
I doubt there's anyone
left in the city
who doesn't know about it.
Oh. Well, that sucks.
But at least I don't have
to waste time explaining it.
So, what the hell are we
waiting for? Let's go get it.
Some of the eager ones have
already started, you know.
It goes without saying the
mafia are gonna be involved,
but there are freelancers
coming, too.
From what I hear, the Yun
Brothers, Big One Emilio,
Ronny CK...
[BAO] Fuck me.
It's like assassin Olympics.
Yeah, and that's not all.
Greentooth Johnny, for example.
What a joke that guy is.
I mean, he actually came in
and ordered an
elephant gun from us.
I don't know what the hell
he was thinking.
[REVY] Someone must've told him
he's up against a
dinosaur or something.
If he uses that,
he'll be scraping this guy
off the fucking ceiling.
[EDA laughing]
[thunder]
[children giggling]
Better get our asses in gear if
we want a chance at that money.
Fifty grand is
too much to ignore.
Yeah, no shit.
So, haven't you got any
other information, Eda?
There's one thing I just heard.
Hmm?
[EDA] Early this morning,
the Caribbean Bar on Buran
Street was completely destroyed.
And I hear that Hotel Moscow
is ready for war.
I guess a collector
of theirs was killed,
so Fry Face is pissed.
[children giggling]
[sirens]
[police radio chatter]
Hey, what a pleasant surprise.
Yeah, sure.
So, is there anything
you want to tell me?
[WATSAP] They found
one of the waiters alive,
though he won't last long.
But he made a statement.
Apparently, these two kids show
up at about four in the morning.
Twins dressed like they
were going to a funeral,
all in black.
And from the sounds of it,
they were spooky little brats,
right out of The Shining
or something.
Well, the bartender takes
one look at 'em and tells 'em,
"This is no place for kids.
You gotta get outta here."
But before he could throw
them out, they pull out your
Bougainvillea Company
business cards and say...
[GRETEL] Most of the time,
we meet our guests
at Miss Balalaika's
place, but...
[HANSEL] We were
told that tonight,
we'd have some
guests to meet here.
Didn't they tell you?
[BARTENDER]
Go around to the back.
[GRETEL] Okay.
Thanks a lot, mister.
Our guests will recognize
us as soon as they see us.
We'll use that corner, okay?
[WATSAP] If at that moment,
the bartender had contacted you,
he might not have been killed.
But he sealed his fate
when he decided not to
disturb you so late at night.
Not long after that,
your collector arrives
at his usual time
to pick up that night's
earnings from the bar.
The collector asks the bartender
how the night's been going.
He tells him it wasn't
a great night and so on.
Nothing special.
Then outta nowhere...
[thunder]
[HANSEL] Hi there.
Would you like to play with us?
Please, mister. Let's play.
Gah! Fuck!
Sakharov! It's them!
[gasping]
They figured it out.
These men actually have
good instincts, sora mea .
They do.
Huh?
[GRETEL] Fratele meu ,
I don't think we're
very good at this yet.
It can't be helped, can it?
So, what do you think
we should do, sora mea ?
I guess we have no choice now.
We'll call upon an angel
for every one of them.
They do say Heaven's
a nice place, after all...
...don't they?
[grunting]
[rapid gunfire]
[GRETEL giggling]
Bad boy.
You mustn't run away.
Sora mea .
Let's bring that
one back with us.
We could play with him.
Sure, fratele meu .
Sounds fun!
Oh, yes, it will be.
[MENSHOV] Ahh... Damn it!
This one's heavy, sora mea .
Can you help me?
But that's a boy's job,
fratele meu .
It's not very ladylike
to carry heavy things.
[WATSAP] Then after they
manage to shove the collector
into their parked car,
they go back into the bar,
where they continue shooting
until they're convinced
everyone's dead!
Did anyone see the license
plate? The make of the car?
A black sedan. A Japanese
make and that's all we know.
'Course, we're currently
investigating its whereabouts.
Oh, yeah, and one more thing...
--Hmm?
--Apparently, they're white,
but not from an
English-speaking country.
They kept addressing each
other in some other language.
Something like,
" Buna seara " or somethin'?
And every time they
addressed each other,
they used these phrases...
Now what the hell was it?
" Fratele meu ," "Sora mea "?
Listen, Watsap--
I want this to stay local,
do you understand?
The last thing we want is for
the military to get involved.
Of course.
Goes without saying.
I like this city the
way it is too, you know.
Oh, yeah. Hey, Balalaika!
Naturally, we'd like to get
in on this little hunt, as well!
The bounty's open to
civil servants too, right?
That man disgusts me. Honestly.
However, it's my mistake.
I simply didn't account
for this type of threat.
I thought if I sent them
out in two-man cells,
they'd be safe.
Sakharov and Menshov were
completely blindsided by this.
No one thought the
assassins were children.
Remember Panjshir though.
Half the enemies we
fought were children.
I've heard that even
souls can accumulate fat.
I suppose that
goes for us, as well.
You're absolutely right,
Kapitän .
Let this be a lesson for us.
Comrade Sergeant.
I cannot allow our forces
to be weakened any further.
Assemble an investigative team
from outside our organization.
People we can afford to lose.
[BORIS] Right.
That now makes eight
soldiers we've had
to put in the ground, comrade.
I never get used to it
no matter how many die.
[BORIS] Since the day
we took our oath,
we've all been prepared
to die in battle.
Like any of us, Sakharov
knew the risks involved.
[BALALAIKA] I won't let
them kill again, Sergeant.
And I will have those brats
pay for Comrade Sakharov's
life with their blood.
I won't rest
until they're dead!
[rain and thunder]
[door creaking open
and bell tinkling]
Damn.
[REVY] So, what's
happening out there?
Has anyone managed
to catch the fish yet?
[DUTCH] Nope. And it ain't
getting any better.
One mistake and
we're all fucked.
I'm talkin' a real shit storm.
Balalaika's planning to use
the services of Visotoniki.
--Visotoniki?
--Crazy bitch.
Does she wanna rip
the whole city apart?
Her commando unit.
In their Ivan language,
they're called the Visotoniki.
These soldiers were
under her command
long before
Hotel Moscow existed.
[marching footsteps]
[ROCK] With her at the head,
each and every one of them
functioned as
a killing machine.
They're all former paratroopers
from the Soviet War
in Afghanistan.
With enough training
to win World War III.
That's what makes them
different from all the others.
They're disciplined,
unified, and show no mercy.
I'll tell you one thing,
I stay the fuck away when
those guys are pissed off.
A two hundred mile
radius, at least.
[beer cans opening]
[GRETEL]
♪ My mother's killed me ♪
[HANSEL]
♪ My father's eating me ♪
[GRETEL] ♪ My brothers and
sisters sit under the table ♪
[HANSEL] ♪ Picking up my bones,
they will bury them ♪
[GRETEL] ♪ Under the cold ♪
Holy shit! What the fuck
are you two doing?!
Changing. See, we can't
wear our old clothes anymore.
The blood got on them and
now it's dried like glue.
So, we needed new clothes.
It's fun, you should try it!
Every time you hammer
a nail into his head,
he twitches
just like a fish.
He still moves, even though
he's not breathing anymore.
I think it's called
spinal reflex or something.
[BIKEY retching]
Do you have any fucking idea
how angry the boss
is right now?!
I only wanted you to
dissect that Ivan bitch!
I never said anything about
kidnapping her associates
and turning them into
goddamn science experiments!
Now here's what
you're gonna do--
you're gonna finish the job
and get the hell outta the city!
'Cause I've fucking had it
with babysitting the two of you!
[thunder]
[BIKEY] I can't believe
those damn brats!
[MAFIA MAN] Talk about
having a fuckin' screw loose!
Moretti! What they did to
that Ivan, it ain't right!
No shit. Worst part is now we
gotta get rid of that corpse.
Not even a cleaner would
do that one. Damn it!
[thunder]
Does this phantom
killer have any idea
what he's dealing with?
If so, he's got to be insane.
[DUTCH] It's rare
even in this place,
but you come across
'em now and again.
Seeds of evil.
Nothin' but trouble.
Even amongst the garbage
of the underworld,
they're considered outsiders.
Usually, these
types will go wild,
cause a lot of damage,
and then wind up dead.
But every so often,
you get one with
instincts like a beast
and a sharp mind
and they manage to survive.
Being unhinged is the only way
these people know how to live.
They leave nothing but death
and destruction in their wake.
[REVY] The one thing they
all have in common is hate.
People like that, they hate
everything and everyone.
But if you ask me,
their real problem is that
they're so filled with hate,
they hit a point where
they can't even remember
what they hate or why they
hated it to begin with.
In the end, they suck
everything around them in
before goin' out
in a blaze of glory.
[phone ringing]
Well, they're the only
ones who know for sure
what's going on in their heads.
If there's one thing you
learn in prison, that's it.
[ROCK] Hmm...
[BENNY] Rock.
She asked for you. It's from the
lady of the hour, so to speak.
Miss Balalaika.
Sora mea , I was wondering...
[GRETEL] What is it?
What should we do?
I know what I wanna do.
We've never tried with
an Ivan before, have we?
No, not that, sora mea .
I mean those guys.
[GRETEL] Oh.
We should be able to get
rid of them eventually.
I hate being scolded and
being hit for no reason.
It makes me wanna cry.
Don't you agree,
fratele meu ?
[ROCK] " Buna seara ."
It's a Romanic language,
italic branch, but...
Hmm...
[BALALAIKA] I thought
given your occupation,
you might recognize it.
Oh, excuse me. I meant
"former" occupation.
[ROCK] Hmm..." Buna seara ."
Okay, then how about this
other phrase--" Fratele meu "?
Anything will help.
Whatever comes to mind.
A place. A name.
I seem to recall someone
from the European branch
teaching me
something like that.
But off the top of my head,
I really couldn't say.
[children giggling]
[ROCK] Vampire!
[BALALAIKA] What'd you say?
What do you mean by that?
[ROCK] Those words...
They have something
to do with vampires.
[GRETEL] It smells very
strongly of blood, fratele meu .
Let's take a bath.
[HANSEL] But it's
such a nice smell.
It's a shame to
waste it, sora mea .
[children giggling]
[BORIS] The Chinese woman
from Lagoon Company
and the sister from the
Ripoff Church are with them.
[BALALAIKA] You may
crush them if necessary.