Go ahead...
Make your report.
We heard gunshots,
we closed with the target.
And this kid was there...
Ah, shit, I'm sorry sir.
I know we didn't need this!
Sir! The kid would be dead
if the First
Sergeant hadn't saved him!
One shot will prove
that he's not really here.
The First Sergeant
made the right call, sir!
Alright, abandon
the pincer attack
and go to a maneuver mission.
Rally point is Dagger Six.
Well, you've made a tough
job even harder, Sergeant.
That's true. But a
child's life was at stake.
Good job, soldier.
Shane...
Listen up, men.
The situation has changed.
Do you think
you're up for this?!
Sir! Yes, sir!
The Young Master... is gone.
He was taken...
by those foxes.
It smell like death in here.
Careful, Shen.
It be real shame if we
lose our rich boy paycheck.
No, don't! Get back here!
Hi-ya!
No!
Roberta!
Don't! She's lost her
fuckin' mind!
Let go! Roberta,
it's me! It's Fabiola!
The Young Master told
me to come and get you!
He and I came here
to find you and ...
Fabiola? Did you find a
newspaper when you tidied up?
The Master was in
the lounge looking for it.
It looks like rain...
I'm gonna fetch
the Young Master
in from the fields
before he gets wet.
Not an option.
That bridge is out.
But that's the only way
out of this place on foot.
Easy there!
We're on your side, kid!
How're you holding up?
Can you understand me?
We're American soldiers, son.
We pulled you out of the
middle of an awful firefight.
You'll be safe with us
until we can get you
to the proper authorities.
You can rest easy now,
you've got my word on that.
Roberta's overdosed on her meds.
I doubt if she'll even
recognize Garcia anymore.
I can't gamble without
knowing all the factors.
If Garcia can't
get her to come back,
I'll have to change
his role in all this.
I'm sorry, kid...
This is asking a lot of you...
I hope you understand.
Everything okay?
You want some water?
What's up, First Sergeant?
Jeez, you're scaring
the boy, you big ape.
What?! Go screw yourself...!
Relax kid, I'm Staff
Sergeant Sanchez.
Nice to meet ya!
You know Horner's a daddy.
He's got a little girl.
Hey, man...!
She's got him wrapped
around her finger.
What'd you have to
tell him all that for?
Hey Burroughs, got a candy bar?
Negatory. But, uh, L.G. might!
Right! He's got
a sweet tooth!
These soldiers...
These are the men!
All of this... all of
this is because of them!
Assuming Garcia doesn't
snap and do something crazy...
We still have to get
the Americans out of here.
For two whole days I
was open about my next move.
I don't exactly know who...
But one of the people
who watches over this city...
is definitely
gonna be calling me.
And they're late.
L. G., tell Bravo and Charlie
we're changing
the rendezvous point.
Yes, sir.
Hey!
Drop it!
The fuck?! Why, kid?!
We don't shoot
children, Sanchez!
Major Caxton...!
He was gonna shoot...!
That's enough,
Horner, let him go.
Boy... Why'd ya do that?
Who are you?
You're no innocent
bystander in this, huh, kid...
No, I'm not...
I'm no bystander!
This... this is all your fault!
You're the ones who ruined our
lives! You ruined everything!
Ruined everything...?
It seems the situation
is even worse than we thought.
Who are you, son?
Don't you remember...?
It was last October...
in Barinas, Venezuela!
Ten people were
killed at a political rally!
One of them...
one of them was my father!
Shit... that was
Executive Order One-Fourteen.
You took the two people I
love the most in the world...
My father...
And someone else, who
might never come back to me!
Here kid, you've earned the
right to take revenge on me.
Stop it, Shane!
You're old enough.
You can decide for
yourself what you wanna do.
What don't you understand?
Let me see it.
It's a puzzle...
There are supposed to
be four things hidden in it.
But as far as I can see,
it's just a picture
of a pair of deer.
Indeed. Emilio brought
it to school to brag about it,
but I think
he's just a big liar.
You shouldn't be so
quick to call people liars.
That's the back.
I know. It's important
to look at things
from many different angles.
See, look here...
Here's a horned owl...
And here's an angel.
And look right there!
It's the Lord Christ!
You're right! But why
couldn't I see them before?!
Probably because you
were looking at the picture
from one side only.
If you want to see
the way things really are,
you have to look at them
from every possible perspective.
Shane, Jesus...!
Lower your weapons!
Now! That's an order!
Oh, it's you. What is it?
That's not much of a hello!
Were you expecting
someone else to show up?
No...
I dropped off all
the goodies you ordered
on the phone this morning.
They'll be waiting
for you when you get there.
Right.
So, how's it going?
You just about done here?
No... it's not over yet.
I'm working on it.
FYI, on my way here I saw some
Ivans running
around on the rooftops.
We've located
the American's main force!
Take your positions
and prepare for combat.
Good to know, but in the end
it shouldn't affect my gamble.
It's the Cold
War all over again!
The proud desantniki
facing down their old enemy!
Rules of Engagement say if he
shoots he's an
enemy hostile, sir!
I gave you an order, dammit!
Major! I'm picking up a lot
of strange radio chatter, sir!
It's in Russian!
Enemy sighted.
I hope Gray Fox
can hear this, Major.
She's right above you.
Better act fast.
I've been hunting
you a long time...!
You better keep
running, little foxy!
Shane!
Major!
Because if you don't... I'll
skin and bleed you like a pig!
Who the hell is she?!
Don't shoot,
you've done enough to her!
Have we...?
She's not well!
Because of what you people
did her mind has been broken!
Young Master...
I thought that
sounded like you...
As soon as the hunt is over,
I'll prepare a
nice cup of tea for you.
I just have a few
more things to take care of.
Target's fallen back.
Well done, Corporal Zachamin.
Unit on the roof,
identify yourself.
We are an autonomous unit
of Soviet Union paratroopers.
And my name? You may
call me Captain Jane Doe.
Listen, Major...
The Bloodhound is still in your
vicinity, retreat immediately.
Rather than
engage with the Americans
and risk killing
each other off...
Balalaika will probably use this
to settle her score with Chang.
The Hong Kong Triad and
Hotel Moscow have been locked
in a struggle over
this city for a long time.
And the battle is far from over.
In their last
encounter before the truce,
Chang got the drop
on Balalaika and shot her.
That's how she came
to owe Dutch a favor.
He saved her life, but the real
reason she's grateful is because
he gave her a second
chance to seek retribution.
Balalaika sees this
as a way to screw Chang.
When it comes to the odds,
you really know your shit!
Judging by the radio chatter,
sounds like everything's
going according to your plan.
So, what's your
next bet, high roller?
Right now, the Americans'
plans have been disrupted.
If they wanna salvage their
operation they'll have to find
some other way
to carry it out.
I intend to
give them that chance.
But what if they pussy
out and cancel the mission?
They won't...
For what it's worth, I think
you're on the right track, Rock.
Canceling the mission
now would make them lose face.
They're too fuckin'
proud to just give up.
I think so too.
If things go well,
all the pieces,
except for Roberta,
should fall into my hands.
And once that
happens all that crap
you so thoughtfully ordered
from me will prove to be
very fucking useful indeed.
And the Americans and
that rich Venezuelan brat
will pay for it all.
Whatever happens,
I still come out ahead!
Might be hope
for you yet, Rock!
Eda!
Huh?
Is that really all
you're getting out of this?
Careful.
You know... On top
of all your other fees...
I'd have thought
the Hong Kong Triad
would be paying you, as well.
Now I see. Sounds
like you're starting to
think about
choosing sides here.
All the mafias claim to
coexist and prosper together...
But Chang is the one
who really runs this city.
Your point?
Chang's not alone.
Who backs him?
No matter how much
respect he's earned here,
he's just a
cheap Hong Kong hood,
there's no way he'd
survive without major support.
And?
I'm looking for the
person who controls Chang...
The one behind the curtain!
The real master of Roanapur!
That's the...!
I wouldn't, Rock.
It's never wise to dive down
to where the
Leviathan waits in the dark.
Besides...
Didn't ya know, Rock?
There are many different gods,
and not all of them get along!
Just learn to relax!
You should give him a call.
They're good. They're keeping
us completely covered.
Yeah, they're also
rude sons of bitches.
Soviets...
Shane, do you
think they're for real?
There is no more U.S.S.R.
And she called
herself "Jane Doe".
Guess she really doesn't
want to tell us who she is.
Look Ray...
I just want to get the hell
out of this fuckin' town before
any more shit happens to us.
Yeah, me too, buddy.
You said to read
this if I lost my way.
Did you know who
was going to have to
do it when you wrote that?!
Hey, Rock!
The boss sure is pissed.
Yeah...
I don't think it's such a good
idea for you to talk to him.
Is that Rock?
Yeah, he wants to talk to you.
Look, Rock, you're
a good guy to work with,
and I don't wanna lose you.
Patch things up!
It's me. I hope you're
proud of yourself, Rock,
you've brought
my insomnia back.
I'm sorry,
Dutch. I really am.
You're polite, but keep
violating our dress code policy
and you're finished.
I am sorry... but this
is way bigger than me now.
Whatever you say, Rock.
You need a lawyer, maybe I
should get you Johnnie Cochran.
Listen Dutch,
I've got a job for you.
An official
Lagoon Company assignment.
The client is
the American government.
The city has no choice now, it's
reached the point of no return.
They have to find someone
who'll take care of this mess
and get the
Americans out of town.
And if we act as the shipping
service and move them out...
then that other huge
problem will leave as well.
Look, I get what
you're saying, Rock.
But you're too
involved in this.
Right now you're just like--
Dutch, when all this mayhem
finally comes to an end...
We could make
a real killing here.
Shit! Hang it up!
Uh, you wanna let
me in on what he said?
I think the maid
isn't the only one
who's gonna need a
shrink after all this crap.
Hello?
Tell him I've thought
about it and I refuse!
It's not him. It's
Chang on the line for ya.
Says he's got a job for us.
See anything, Spooky?
Isn't that
your Garcia kid there?
That suck...!
Our rich boy pay-check
is with American GIs!
That kid's a
real pain in the ass.
There's just a couple.
We could take them
out. Whatcha got?
I got these.
Fuckin' A.
Yeah, it's still inside you.
When did you get hit?
Uh, when that screaming
banshee swooped down on us.
I threw myself
in front of the boy.
Okay...
Look like big fella in
middle can't move so good.
I'll deal with
him and black guy.
You take last one,
he look like he the boss.
Alright, we kill these
fuckers on the count of three.
Ready? One, two, three...
You motherfuckers!
I need these arms for
work and you shot both of them!
Two-Hands!
I have a message
from the Captain!
"This is not your war,
it is ours alone.
We will not tolerate
outside interference.
Next time, we will shoot you
in the head!" End of message.
Aw, fuck!
Young Master...
Gentlemen...
Look.
No sign of any booby-traps.
Heh, runs like a dream!
The boy's map brought
us to this location.
Didn't expect to
find you here, Will.
I'm here because
this snitch I know told me
about a neutral
party who'd help us.
And you probably
won't believe this,
but it ended up being the
Catholic church up on the hill.
Nothing would surprise me now.
We even managed
to get a boat to
bring the team to
the area of operations.
Fire Team B coming in.
Good!
I'm sorry about this, Major...
But we can't cancel the mission.
Fire team C's here, sir.
Right!
Do a fast roll call
and get everyone
squared away in the trucks!
I don't like this,
but we can't abort now.
That's weird.
Looks like we
got two kids now.
What? Just bring them both.
It was like a
damn warzone back there,
and still no sign of the cops!
Just five blocks over and
the city's open for business!
Major.
Yes, Captain...
Thanks for covering
our asses there.
It was our pleasure, Major.
But truth be told,
you and your men are the ones
that we really wanted to fight.
We've wanted that ever since we
left the civilized world behind.
My men and I
have waited and waited
for a great war to come...
Since the days we stumbled
onto the sands of Afghanistan.
You fought in Afghanistan?
Our country's
humiliation was Vietnam.
Different nations,
different battlegrounds...
My men saw the same things
and fought just as desperately
as your soldiers did!
But that is the past...
Now, we've regressed
so far that our energies are
wasted on squabbles
with petty hoodlums instead of
honest war-time combat!
I despise being
one of the walking dead
and I am filled
with envy for those who
are still in the
land of the living.
At the very least,
I wanted you to know
who you were dealing with.
The discipline and power
of a truly elite fighting force!
And know that if
you had ever faced us,
we'd have
taught you real fear.
Well, Major...?
Hold on...
Looks like you're out of time.
Captain, just a minute.
Safeties off, men!
Concentrate your
fire to the left!
Stand-by to engage!
I am sorry, Major.
The men cannot wait.
We will give
you a proper send-off.
Prepare the salute!
Take aim! Fire!
All shots on target, Captain.
So. How was that?
First class work.
Your forces were
masterfully positioned
and the skill with
which your men launched
the RPG assault was...
impressive.
Those are kind words and
it's a considerable honor to
receive your compliment.
But tell me...
If we're both from the
elite units of our nations...
Then why did our country
treat us like outcasts?!
Captain... Perhaps it's none
of my business, but were you...
discharged for an "illness?"
I'm not surprised
that you would think that.
It was called
a "voluntary discharge"
but the reality is I deserted.
It was an easy
decision to make.
There was an illegal
international mission...
I saved a child
in a refugee camp.
And that's what
the media reported.
All this happened in
Nineteen eighty-six. April.
Now, hurry up and get the
hell out of this city, Major.
And make sure that
I never see you here again.
There are just so
many things going on.
That goes for this city... and
the inside of my stupid head.
What exactly am I
trying to accomplish?
Rock, you still know what you're
fuckin' doing here, right?
Yeah. Of course I do.
Good to hear.
You won't be able
to count on me, though.
That's alright.
From this point on,
that won't be a problem.
That right?
Yeah. It'll be okay.
It's scary,
he's almost too efficient.
Fake registration, all river
passes, boat licenses for
three countries, and
an official NGO permit.
With press cards for
all of us and enough weapons
for our passengers
to fight a small war.
In other words,
he ordered all this from
the Church and they delivered?
For the finishing touch he
even had Mr. Chang call me up
to commission the job.
Shit! I couldn't
refuse the guy, damn it!
Rock was a businessman,
but this is pretty hardcore.
Lagoon just left the harbor.
If she's still alive,
the maid will definitely leave
the city to chase after them.
I love it when
a plan comes together
and all the
pieces fit just right.
The way you manipulated
that Russian battle axe was
a work of art, and that Japanese
pussy did all your dirty work
just 'cause you
poked him in his pride!
Now don't take
this the wrong way...
I didn't understand at first,
but now I finally get why
the Dailow chose to
elevate someone like you.
A dirty cop who
killed his partners.
You've got some
big fucking balls.
Stop, you'll make me blush.
Gentlemen, I'm the
captain of this ship.
We're gonna refuel
out on the open sea.
After that, I'll take
you where you're going.
I'm Caxton, the leader here.
Forgive my bluntness, Captain,
but can my men and I trust you?
Think what you want.
I didn't want to meet
that female cyborg ever again...
But on the other hand,
this gig has turned into
a pretty good paying job.
It sucks...
But don't worry, I will honor
my contract with you guys.
I'll take you
where you wanna go.
You've got
bigger problems, boys,
because I seriously
doubt that woman's dead.
So, uh, he's in
a bit of a bad mood...
but don't you
guys worry about him.
He could do this course
half-drunk and blindfolded.
He knows this route?
He was stationed here
on a river patrol boat
during the Vietnam War.
This boat's been contracted
to head up the Mekong River...
We'll enter at the delta
and then make our way upstream
to where the borders of
Thailand, Burma and Laos meet.
In other words...
we're headed straight for the
heart of the Golden Triangle.
One more thing...
Everything behind this
door is my personal property.
That means it's off limits.
Thank you for choosing to
fly with Bangkok Airlines today.
This flight will be leaving from
Don Muang International Airport
and landing at Mandalay
Airport at 2:30pm, Myanmar time.
I do declare!
That's one powerful odor!
Guess we didn't have
time for a shower today,
heaven knows those foxes
are quick little rascals!
At any rate, I see you found
the airline ticket
I left in your bunker.
Good for you!
I set it up so that,
despite your somewhat
suspicious appearance, security
would let you through the gate.
Within thirty-six...
Who are you?
Are you...
a bounty hunter...?!
Because if you are...!
You're being too
fucking loud, you moron!
Shut up and listen!
I'm trying to tell you where
your stupid foxes are going!
And I even made all the
arrangements to get you there!
I appreciate your
assistance, whoever you are.
Oh? You do have manners.
After all this is finished
and my hunt is complete...
I will reward you
with a painless death.
This is the spot...
Drop anchor and
wait for the fuel boat here.
Tomorrow we'll
head up the Mekong.
Mini-maid...
Time for lights out.
What were you doing?
Studying English idioms.
I don't understand
some of the words you use.
Nose to the grindstone...
And what's the
little lord up to?
He's down at
the stern by himself.
The Young Master
keeps whispering that
Roberta is still alive.
Yeah, I think so, too.
And because she's alive,
I think Rock is planning to
pull off
another dumb-ass stunt.
But look at
the shape I'm in.
I'm all fucked up.
If anything happens...
We'll have to
rely on your guns.
I know we were the ones
who asked him to help...
But now I'm starting to think
that Senor Rock is dangerous.
He planned all along to
have the Young Master
meet up with the Americans.
I think it hurt him... a lot.
Huh, like I'm always saying...
Rock's best suited to sitting
on a beach with a cold drink
soaking up the rays, not
gambling with people's lives.
Sometimes people take on
a little more
than they can handle.
Garcia paid the price.
If you think he can't handle it,
then why don't
you toughen him up?
Why haven't you already?
What do you want from him?
Ah, so that's it.
What's "it"?
There's a quality about
him that you really admire,
but you're afraid that if you
dig too deep under the surface
you might be wrong.
Me, admire him?!
You're fuckin' deluded!
You're the
one who's... deluded.
When I look at him, I don't see
the guy you keep talking about.
I think you don't want
to see his true nature...
because then you would
lose your shining knight.
You think he's this
gentle and peaceful guy
who just sits in the sun.
But if those things
are important to you...
then maybe you two
should go to South America
and open a
little vegetable stall.
But you two are
never going to do that.
You're fuckin' crazy...
We're different,
but you think we come
from the exact same place.
And it's obvious that you
try to see him as the
opposite of who you are.
That's because you want
to be saved by some hero.
Well, I'm not one to
talk since I've had to use
and deceive him
to get what I wanted.
I did it all to
get our head maid back.
And to help the
Young Master heal from this...
So he can know real peace.
How are we different?
What?
A minute ago, you said
that we're different.
So tell me how
we're different exactly.
You've got the
eyes of a wild dog.
In my neighborhood...
I saw a lot
of people like you.
Your family was completely
dysfunctional, wasn't it...?
So?
But my family wasn't like that.
My father worked
minimum wage at a parking lot.
My mother would never tolerate
any of her
children committing a sin.
When I stole a CD player
to give to my younger
brother as a present...
my mother beat
me black and blue.
That sounds
like abuse to me.
Whatever they did,
they did out of love!
Oh, come on.
You grew up picking
through garbage in one of
the poorest fuckin'
cities in the world.
Don't tell me you've
convinced yourself that you
and your Young Master are
birds of a fuckin' feather.
Does the world look like
the Garden of Eden
to you, Mini-maid?
Ah, this is pointless!
You really are
dumb, aren't you?!
You little bitch!
Who are you calling dumb?!
You don't even
know how stupid you are!
The funny thing is...
You think Rock is completely
innocent, but he's not.
Garcia... we need to talk.
It's about our next move.
All the actors
are on the stage.
I don't know...
You want me to help you again?
Indeed.
I even have a
little prop for you.
It's all been worked
out. You're the key, Garcia.
The golden key.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
We are gonna hit the jackpot!
Benny, Chang is gonna lose!