[whistle blowing]
[ROCK] Not so long ago,
I was a businessman in Tokyo.
Now I work for a shipping
company in the South China Sea.
That's it. All the crates
are accounted for.
Now could I please get
you to sign this for me?
Um, excuse me, could
somebody please sign this?
There's nothing
particularly special
about this little shipping
company. Though, at times,
we do brush up against
the law to get the job done.
Huh?
Everything under control, Rock?
[ROCK] We're good. And I even
got them to sign for it.
[DUTCH] We're also transporting
additional cargo for them.
Did you get it?
[ROCK] About that. I... um...
Well, yeah, I did receive
that shipment from them.
[DUTCH] Is there a problem?
If not, then have them
use a crane again
to get you and
the goods down here.
--[ROCK] Got it.
--[REVY] So, the troublemaker's
making use of himself, huh?
On second thought, I don't think
anything's really changed,
has it? The only thing
that's useful about him
is his white-collar look. It
makes him perfect for this job.
So far, anyway.
Wait, let me guess... Is he
worried about that little cargo
we're taking back with us?
[DUTCH] Looks that way.
Pathetic.
After all, it's just a cartel's
little errand we're running,
so what's the big deal?
[ROCK] I counted those
crates we delivered
like you wanted me to.
And I brought that shipment
we're taking back with us, too.
But are you sure... he's it?
[DUTCH] Once we
arrive in Hat Yai,
we're handing him
over to some buyer
designated by the
Colombian Mafia.
Revy, put him in
a cabin for now.
Fine.
Alright, let's go, kid.
Hey! You don't
wanna piss me off.
Over here. Come on.
Move your little ass!
[horn sounding]
He actually looked like he
was gonna puke or something.
You can tell he's
still an amateur.
[seagulls]
[DUTCH] Rock.
We're nothing more
than delivery boys.
All we do is take shipments to
their designated destinations.
That's where our
responsibilities end.
--Understand?
--I got it.
You don't have to
worry about me.
I won't get too
attached to the boy.
That's good to hear.
[REVY] Now you've asked
for it, you little shit!
[DUTCH]
Rock.
[REVY] How about I
show you what you had
for breakfast this morning?!
Sorry, but would you
mind taking over
babysitting duties for now?
As you can see, not a lot
of maternal instinct there.
We can't exactly deliver
the shipment with holes in it.
[REVY] Take advantage
of my kindness, will ya?!
--Revy!
--That's right!
What the fuck are
you looking at?!
That's enough!
[REVY] He doesn't deserve
something as nice as a cabin.
We should be chaining him up
and throwing him in the hold.
Little shit.
We're in the middle of the sea
right now. He can't escape.
What the hell do we
need chains for?
Shut up!
Uh, listen. It's just
for a bit longer,
but we are gonna be
traveling together.
Maybe it's too much to ask,
but could you stop
throwing food at me?
You can't fool me.
Santa Maria sees right through
your friendly talk. You liar.
Well, I can see how my words
wouldn't mean much to you,
since I'm helping
with this kidnapping.
You're not...anything like
that mean tattooed lady
or that big black guy, are you?
You actually seem
like a normal person.
I guess. But the truth is I'm
really just a crook in training.
The men who put me on the boat
didn't tell me where I'm going
or what's gonna happen to me.
They're planning to sell me
off somewhere, aren't they?
You worried?
I'll be fine. My father would
never let anything happen to me.
Father? But aren't you
supposed to be an orphan?
Who told you that?
It was probably the cartel.
They're a bunch of big liars.
My father's the head of one
of the great thirteen families
of South America.
The eleventh patriarch
of the Lovelace household.
He is Diego José
San Fernando Lovelace.
And I'm Garcia, his only
son. When I'm old enough,
I'll become the next
head of the Lovelace family.
[ROCK] If you're looking for
pity, you won't find it here.
If you're gonna tell lies,
you could at least come up
with a better one than that.
I don't want pity!
Don't be stupid.
What good would it do
me to lie to you now?
You know, you're a
pretty unlikable kid.
So, where'd you hear
the name Lovelace, anyway?
For your information,
it's the least noble house
of the thirteen families.
Although, that does make it
a little more believable.
So what if things haven't been
going too well for us lately?
We're still managing to get by,
just like we always do.
My father is a man
of good character.
He never got involved
in anything illegal.
[birds chirping]
Business wasn't going well,
but the plantations were stable.
Until the mafia came, that is.
[ROCK] And you're
trying to tell me
that you were kidnapped
by that mafia?
You have a gift for making
up stories, kid. Not bad.
They came one day and
tried to force my father
to sell our land.
A geological survey showed
that we had lanthanides there.
When my father refused to sell,
we saw what they
were really like.
They came to our farms
and harassed us.
But my father refused
to be intimidated by them.
And that's how I ended up here.
Lanthanides?
It's also called rare earth.
Don't you know your
periodic table?
Well... Where did you
learn a word like that, kid?
You still think I'm lying,
don't you? Well, that's okay.
It's just that
it's not that easy.
What can I do to
make you believe me?
Why don't you tell me what else
you know about rare earth?
You know, lanthanides?
Lutetium, atomic number 71.
That's what was
found on our land.
It's used as a fixing
agent for ceramics.
How's that?
Not enough?
I have another
question for you.
It's well-known that the
Lovelace household has a dog.
About that dog...
Tell me what you know.
That's an easy question.
That dog became a member
of our family six years ago.
His name is Lazlo and he's
a white Volpino Italiano.
Revy. Rock's taking too long.
Huh. I bet he's in there
right now rocking him to sleep.
He's gonna get all emotional.
He's probably gonna come up
here and give us a sob story
and ask us to let him go.
What'd I say?
Look at those eyes.
Not cool. I don't
like how this feels.
We need more information.
After we dock, I think
we should wait
before handing him
over to the mafia.
It's obvious the
cartel lied to us.
If they were lying about him,
it can only mean
there's gonna be trouble.
[REVY] Rock.
Don't take pity on our cargo.
You'll feel like total shit
if you start imagining
all the places that
kid could end up.
But... as long as our
company sees a profit,
then there's really
no problem. Understand?
His life has nothing
to do with us after that.
Even if there is no justice,
the world's gonna
keep on turning.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't pity him.
But I'm also concerned
that our client lied to us.
I worked in the resource
procurement department.
So, I know a lot about
rare earth and rare metals.
And everything he says about
the Lovelace family checks out.
I remember seeing
a number of reports
from our South
American division--
details about their
family structure.
Very impressive. That is
so interesting, Rock.
Aren't you just the
brilliant businessman?
Seriously, I think we should
put your picture on a fucking
employee-of-the-month plaque
and hang it up right here.
Either way, it's
still up to Dutch.
He gets the final say on this.
I just don't get it.
The minute they got the kid,
they could've demanded
a ransom right then.
And they would've
got what they wanted.
Is there any reason for
them to keep it a secret
and sell him off?
[REVY] I dunno why
they'd keep it a secret.
But I can think of a good reason
why they'd wanna sell the kid.
If you ask me, they probably did
it cuz they were pissed off.
If there's one thing
all mafias have in common,
it's that they hate having
shit rubbed in their faces.
They're not gonna let something
like that go unpunished.
Know what I mean?
[DUTCH] Hmm... Revy,
if their pride's at stake,
then this is gonna
be a real hassle.
And we definitely don't
want any part of that.
I think I'm gonna put
a little extra insurance
on our shipment
before we deliver it.
I'll ask Balalaika to
do some background checks.
[BALALAIKA] My, my.
It's quite rare to have
you asking a favor, Dutch.
[DUTCH] I need a
little background
on the Manisarera Cartel
and the Lovelace family.
Can you dig that up for us?
[BALALAIKA] Huh?
We actually just
picked up a job
involving the
Manisarera Cartel.
Your timing is
impeccable, Dutch.
[DUTCH] Thanks. I owe you one.
But since we're
still in the process
of setting up our insurance,
don't stir things up too much.
[BALALAIKA] Well,
that's impossible.
What?
You know the way
this business works.
When things get stirred up,
they're stirred up
like a typhoon.
[DUTCH] Just do your best.
Keep it cool.
[BALALAIKA] Very well. Shall I
get back to you at your office?
[DUTCH] No. We'll be having
a drink at the Yellow Flag.
You can find us there.
Hmm...
Alright then, Rock.
There's one more thing
we need to check out
before this thing
goes any further.
I'm talking about
daddy Lovelace.
Is he the type who's capable
of sending out private troops
to rescue his son, or was
the kid just bluffing us?
I don't think so.
Financially speaking,
they can't afford more
than one personal servant
for the entire household
at this point.
A servant? What kind?
[ROCK] An ordinary housemaid.
So, do you think the
maid's gonna rush in
to try and save the
little prince or what?
That would be fun.
[horn sounding]
[seagulls]
Huh?
[MAN 1] What did you just say?
I said I'm just a lonely
soul who's come here
from South America and I
require your assistance.
If you could direct me,
I'm in search of a place where
I can find my fellow countrymen.
Might you know of
such a place nearby?
So, by "fellow countrymen,"
you mean from your country?
[ROBERTA] Why yes, of course.
Um, this little lady's
countrymen, huh?
[MAN 2] Hey, she could mean...
But there are no other
"countrymen" of hers
in this area, right?
Listen, lady, I'm afraid
we can't give you
that sorta info ourselves.
Perhaps you might direct me
to someone who could tell me...
[MAN 2] Well, miss,
there is a place where
you might be able
to find out...
But it's like one big viper pit,
if you catch my drift...
I do not mind.
I'll go to this place
if I can find out about
my fellow countrymen.
[MAN 3] I really wouldn't
recommend it, sweetheart.
[ROBERTA] Please do not worry.
[REVY] We're here. On dry land.
Huh? Would you get
moving already?!
C'mon. What are you,
a schoolyard bully?
Don't forget, you used to
be a brat once upon a time.
[REVY] Yeah? I don't remember
getting paid to babysit.
This is a fucking joke.
Revy.
[REVY] Move your ass!
Alright, isn't that enough?
Oh, what? You too now?
Wait, let me guess--
you're gonna treat him nice
and get a job at his house?
Guess that makes sense.
Just look at you.
You'd definitely be better
off as some stuck-up butler
than as a sailor.
That's for damn sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whatever you say, Revy.
[REVY] You'll be asking him,
"Master, how would you
like your Mint Julep?
I sure hopes you like it."
Hell, you can be just
like Old Black Joe...
Must be nice to be surrounded
by dozens of servants all day.
Ha!
[GARCIA]
Like I told you before,
my family only has
the one servant.
She's a maid and
her name's Roberta.
But she's not very good at
cleaning or doing chores.
We don't serve milk here.
[ROBERTA] Then may I
have a glass of water?
I only arrived here today
and I don't know my way around.
I'm in search of a
Colombian friend of mine.
Do you know where
I might find...
Order a real drink.
This is a bar, you dumb bitch.
I only arrived here today
and I don't know my way around.
I am in search of a
Colombian friend of mine.
Do you know where I might find
my fellow Colombians
in this town?
Or could you help me
find the authorities?
It would be a great help.
Lady, does this place look like
a fucking tourist center to you?
Do you see me handing out maps?
[ROBERTA] No.
She's always been very clumsy.
And it's true, she can't
clean or do chores.
But still, Roberta's a
lot stronger than you are
and she's gonna save me!
That's gotta be the funniest
thing I've heard all day!
She's not gonna throw a fucking
teacup at me, is she? Oooh!
If this turns out to be true,
then I'll believe
anything you say, kid.
Even if you said Jesus rode
a chopper across Route 66!
And have you seen her
when she was being strong?
I haven't. But I do remember
there was this one time...
[dog barking]
[GARCIA] We lived together
at my father's house.
It was just the three of us--
my father, Roberta, and me.
It was a peaceful life.
[ROBERTA yells]
[GARCIA] I didn't have many
friends to play with there,
so Roberta would
always play with me.
I especially loved to
arm wrestle with her.
Probably because I could
beat Roberta every time.
And even though she never won,
she was always a
good sport about it.
The two of us were
out in the garden
arm wrestling on that day, too.
And then...
...they came.
To threaten my father.
[birds chirping]
[GARCIA] Somehow,
she knew what was going on
long before I ever did.
The moment she sensed that
they were coming to our house,
her arm suddenly stiffened.
I used every ounce of strength
I had in me to try and beat her,
but...
[knocking]
Her arm wouldn't move.
It was like steel.
All those times, she'd been
losing to me on purpose.
And that's when I realized
there was a good reason
why Roberta played the part
of the weak and timid maid.
I found out then.
[chattering in background]
Hmm?
[footsteps]
Huh?
[gasps]
[BORIS] Fallen nobility.
The wife died four years ago.
Pictured here are the father,
Diego, his only son, Garcia,
and their one servant.
She's a housemaid
and a caretaker for the boy.
[BALALAIKA] I don't like this.
This isn't good.
[BORIS] Ma'am?
Comrade Sergeant,
take a look at her eyes.
Don't you notice anything?
[BORIS] The eyes of a soldier.
[BALALAIKA] That is correct,
Sergeant. And that's not all.
She's one hell of a rabid dog.
Woman, I've got
business with you.
I hear some crazy bitch
dressed up like a maid
is asking all over town
where she can find
the Colombian mafia.
Wearing this crazy outfit
you'd only see in a movie.
Any pendejo would remember
someone in an outfit like that.
Well, now that you've
called us here,
what the fuck do you want?
Who the hell are you, huh?!
I'm glad you came, as it was
my intention that you find me.
You are from the Manisarera
Cartel, is that not correct?
I am a servant of
the Lovelace family
and I have come a
long way to be here.
I have a few questions
I'd like to ask.
Please excuse me,
but I'm afraid I may have no
other choice but to be rude.
[ABREGO] Ha, ha.
Did you hear that?
"Be rude," she says.
What a crazy bitch!
[CARTEL MAN 1] What?
With your umbrella?
[ROBERTA] I'm very sorry, but
I will not be able to hold back.
Please excuse me.
And... I hope you
enjoy yourselves.
Roberta!
[ROCK] I see it now.
That maid is a killer
robot from the future!