[ROCK] Graduating from
a national university,
I somehow managed to make my
way into the corporate world.
This is a businessman's town.
I get my ass kicked
by my boss all day.
But at the same time, I hope
to be in his place someday.
It's the only way to
maintain your sanity here.
This is the city of winter,
where I once lived.
It all seems so far away.
Right now, all that's in front
of me is the shimmering water
of the South China Sea.
The stirring winds of--
[grunting]
[DUTCH] Alright, Mr. Japanese.
I'll ask you one more time--
the package you got from the
Asahi Industry headquarters
in Tokyo, the one
you're in charge of until
you hand it over to the chief
in Borneo. This is it, right?
Yeah, but what
I want to know is--
We're all done with you now.
You've given us what we wanted.
Dutch, this is
a pain in the ass.
I say we kneecap this pussy.
They'll be no secrets
after that.
There's no need.
That one disc is more than
enough for the compensation.
[REVY] You call
that compensation?
[BENNY] Dutch. Hey, Dutch.
You through with them yet?
There's something heading
straight for us from Subic Bay.
It's probably a patrol boat
from the Filipino Navy.
Don't panic, Benny-boy.
It's all been taken care of.
Start the engines.
[engines revving]
Now listen up, Gentlemen!
We're gonna disappear and
then you'll all be free to go.
But I'm warning you--
the deal's off if anyone
decides to come after us.
What you see there
is a torpedo launcher.
If you don't want to float home
on what's left of your ship,
I recommend you stay put
for the next half hour.
After that, you're free
to do as you wish.
We're gonna live.
Why are you looking so relaxed?
You're gonna tag along
with us, dumbass.
You're joking.
You're joking, right?
Now shut up and walk.
[ROCK] You're joking, right?!
Japan is drifting farther away.
This is Black Lagoon to
Balalaika. Can you hear me?
[BALALAIKA]  Just fine, Dutch.
What about the catch?
[DUTCH] I've got it, of course.
I admire smart work, Dutch.
[DUTCH] The trade-off
goes as planned.
Yes, just as I promised.
[phone dialing]
[phone ringing]
Connect me to Tokyo.
[EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR]
Well, Kageyama,
as Resource Investigation
Division Manager,
how do you explain this?
[KAGEYAMA] Regarding the case
we've recently been informed of,
let me explain the situation
to you in greater detail.
Today at approximately 4:00 PM,
a certain Bougainvillea
Trade Company contacted us,
wishing to negotiate
an agreement
for the safe return
of our disc,
which was stolen from
the Melanesia earlier today.
[VICE PRESIDENT] What's
the story on this company?
They're the Russian Mafia.
Well, to be exact,
they're a front for the branch
that aims to take top position
after completely displacing
the Chinese Mafia
from Southeast Asia.
What are they looking
for, specifically?
Do they want money?
[KAGEYAMA] Most likely,
they're out to Southeast Asia
where the barter is
going to take place.
They no doubt wish to take
part in some of our more
unsavory trade activities
in that area.
It's a regrettable development.
Blackmail.
It's shameful that we're
vulnerable to blackmail.
Based on what
we've heard so far,
it would seem to me
that at this point, anyway,
they don't really know
what's on the disc.
[VICE PRESIDENT] If they ever
found out, it would lead
to the worst scandal in
Asahi Industries' history.
[EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR] Indeed.
We have just received
a report from Jakarta.
According to a local Chinese
merchant we've been speaking to,
the Russian Mafia has yet
to receive the disc.
It is still in the
hands of the pirates
that attacked the Melanesia.
This is our chance.
We simply cannot trust
the word of the mafia on this.
We must get the disc at all
costs before it reaches them.
[MANAGING DIRECTOR] Before
it reaches them? But how?
I understand.
The board will leave this matter
in your hands, Kageyama.
Choosing what actions to take
will also be your
responsibility.
Revy, what in the hell
are you planning to do
with this hostage now that
you brought him with us, huh?
Come on!
You don't get it, do ya?
You just don't get it,
do you, Dutch?
Think about it--we're getting
paid twenty grand for this job.
Only twenty grand!
What's wrong with collecting
a bonus by asking for a ransom?
You're being too simpleminded.
--You want to die, Benny?!
--Not really.
[DUTCH] So, who's going to
negotiate with Japan? You?
Do you have their phone number?
How 'bout a bank account
to receive the ransom payment?
Fine then! We'll just shoot
his ass and throw him overboard.
[ROCK] Stop it!
[DUTCH] Damn it!
Don't damage the ship.
[REVY] Shut up!
Dutch... Dutch, I get it.
You get what?
I get your point now,
so let me go.
Okay, Revy, let's play it cool.
I'm alive. I don't know why,
but somehow, I'm alive.
[DUTCH] Alright, alright.
Let's go topside for a smoke.
[ROCK] What's going
to happen to me?
I guess we'll make contact
with your company somehow
and then we'll try
to set up a trade.
There's going to be
a ransom, huh?
This will go on
my permanent record.
But we have our own priorities
and that's just the way it is.
Getting the disc to our client
has got to come first.
So, there's a client?
Now I get it.
We're nothing more
than delivery boys.
Sometimes, we'll break the rules
to put food on the table,
but that's business.
[ROCK] I guess this must be
what they call the
Stockholm Syndrome.
Right now, I feel like
this big guy next to me
is the only person I can
trust in the entire world.
[DUTCH] What's your name?
Okajima. Rokuro Okajima.
[BOARD MEMBER 3] What's
the name of that employee?
[KAGEYAMA] It's Okajima,
Sir. Rokuro Okajima.
[FUJIWARA] My managerial skills
are completely to blame
for all of this, Sir.
[BOARD MEMBER 3] Why didn't
you tell me about this earlier?
[FUJIWARA] I was only
informed recently, myself, Sir.
And because there were
no other employees
we could trust with
this sensitive information,
we ended up losing valuable
time in confirming our sources.
That's enough. Kageyama,
what are your thoughts?
Our company is currently
facing a crisis.
And I'm afraid we can't accept
any more delays at this point.
The EO Company,
with whom we've made a
confidential contract,
has already sent
their professionals.
Well, it was your
responsibility, after all.
But I do feel bad
for this employee.
What's his name?
It's Okajima, Sir.
Rokuro Okajima.
So, you gonna join us, Rock?
"Rock"?
[BENNY] I think he means you.
Huh.
So, you comin' or what?
What? Where are you going?
Some place to get a drink.
Don't you want to come?
But... aren't I a hostage?
--[BENNY] We're leaving.
--[ROCK] Wait, I'm coming, too.
But where on earth am I?
[chattering]
[ROCK] I just don't get it.
Why is there a gun
on every table?
Is this the so-called bar
at the end of the world
you see in westerns?
[DUTCH] Good analogy.
This place was founded by the
Southern Vietnamese soldiers
who survived the war.
They started taking in
fugitive soldiers, too,
and before we knew it, the
place had gone straight to hell.
Hookers, junkies,
mercenaries, hit men.
Irredeemable criminals,
every one of them.
Don't like it?
Japanese pubs...
[SHOP WOMAN] Order of
mackerel, chicken cartilage...
I don't know. I just love
those unguarded smiles.
Places like this...
Shut the fuck up before I toss
your ass out of here, damn it!
[ROCK] I usually try to
avoid confrontations.
[DUTCH] Your expression
says it all.
Benny, I'm gonna make a call.
[BENNY] Sure.
Dutch is a little bit unusual.
After being around him for
two years, all I can tell you
is that he's tough,
intelligent, and eccentric.
You can give up on
trying to figure him out.
Got it.
You seem different from
the other people around here.
Where'd you come from?
A college in Florida.
I was fooling around
and managed to piss off
the mafia and the FBI
at the same time.
And then...
[REVY] Yours truly stepped
in and saved his ass
before it was stuffed in
a bag and thrown overboard.
Stop the worthless storytelling.
You're too young
to be reminiscing.
Now, it's time for all
of us to go shot for shot.
We came all the way
here for a drink.
Let's talk about something
a little more interesting,
Mr. Japanese.
This is...
You ask me, beer's
no different from piss.
That stuff will
never get you drunk.
A real man takes rum.
But if you don't
even have the balls
to keep up with a woman...
...then I'm not going
to try and force you.
Though I might want to
put a little dress on you
with some pretty ribbons
and take you out
for a night of dancing. Hm?
As a rule, I hate chugging
drinks like some teenager,
but I'll make an exception.
[gulping]
I was forced to
drink at college.
We're forced to drink
at company social events.
Never underestimate a
Japanese businessman.
Why you!
Hey, Bartender!
Bring us all the Bacardi
you got right now!
Jeez. And all this time here,
I was thinking you
didn't like confrontations.
No shit. That's definitely
not good news.
Yeah, go on.
[BALALAIKA]
Something wasn't right
about Asahi
Industries' response,
so I left out some bait and
a Chinese rat went right for it.
In fact, I'm talking to him now.
[DUTCH] Who's on the move?
[BALALAIKA] One moment.
What's your owner's name?
Loud and clear.
Sh-Shingian!
Shingian Wan Taikei!
He sent his troops
to assassinate them.
He's sent mercenaries
to Roanapur.
Hear that?
[DUTCH] Yeah. Not good.
Tell me the number and
affiliation of those soldiers.
Speak up and make it fast.
[CHINESE MAN]
Guys from Extra Order,
a mercenary contracting agency!
I don't know how many there are.
The EO Company scouts
experienced war junkies.
[DUTCH] Just our luck.
Try not to die.
Let's get started.
[crowd cheering]
Huh?
Okay. Let's do it, boys.
Let's crash this party.
Give anyone trying to
escape an extra asshole.
Make sure there are only corpses
left when we're done here.
Revy, if these assholes
are your friends,
then you'd better
deal with them.
Don't know 'em.
Wow, you've bulletproofed
the bar, huh?
Yep. It can handle
up to fifty caliber.
[DUTCH] Revy?
[REVY] I'm okay!
Benny?
[BENNY] Miraculously, I'm alive!
--And Rock?
--[ROCK] Dead! People are dead!
I went to all the trouble
of graduating college
and got a job with a big
corporation. Where am I now?
This isn't fair.
[REVY] Don't cry, dipshit.
Don't you know you gotta
enjoy life or it'll slip away?
Revy! I think now's a good time
to show 'em why
you're called "Two-Hands."
[EO CAPTAIN] Secure the
building. I heard voices.
And there's nothin' I
hate more than survivors.
What a great line.
Got 'em for you, Dutch!
Don't come back here,
Revy! You pain in the ass!
How many times have
you destroyed my bar?
You owe me for all this
damage, you understand?
Or else I'm going to
weld your asshole shut
and make you a new
one on your head.
Got it. Dutch!
She's... smiling.
Hate to break it to you,
but at this rate,
I'd say trading you
is no longer an option.
Then what's gonna happen to me?
You weren't part of
our plans to begin with.
How 'bout we just
part ways here?
That's not fair.
I'm gonna die here.
Take me with you!
Fine then. But we can't
have you slowing us down.
Revy, we're leaving!
Gotcha.
Get in!
Take this, cocksuckers!
Hey, Dutch. Bao
was so pissed off,
he looked like a steaming pot.
He said unless we pay him back,
he's going to weld our assholes.
That's scary. I think
I'm gonna cry.
What the hell is this?
A movie? Am I in a movie?
Don't be stupid.
This is way more entertaining
than Hollywood's ever gonna be.
Captain, we've got sixteen
dead, eight wounded.
I'm sorry, Sir. We thought
they were a bunch of punks.
We underestimated them.
Well, Storm, we're not dealing
with some random amateurs here.
In fact, they scored quite
a victory against us today.
In Liberia, all we
had to shoot at
were tired old men
and little brats.
Too slow and no
fight left in 'em.
But these guys
are full of energy.
I've been waiting for
something like this.
[DUTCH] If we
maintain this speed,
we should reach
Belawan Port by daybreak.
We'll meet Balalaika there.
So, Rock...
Huh?
Benny's getting in touch
with your company as we speak.
Huh?
What the hell? So, there is
a way to get this done.
[DUTCH] If negotiations
don't go well,
we're going to have to leave
you in Malaya. I'm sorry.
The place is crawling with
lowlifes and bandits,
but you should survive
for a while. Okay?
Are you serious?!
You bring me this far
just to let me die?
What is this? After
dragging me everywhere?
You're the ones who
brought me here.
The least you could do
is leave me some place safe.
I wouldn't push your luck.
First, you come crying to us,
then you want to
use us like a taxi?
I know, why don't I do
you a fucking favor
and show you what
color your brain is?
Wait!
And we're connected.
We're using an assault dial,
so the line should
be totally secure.
Rock, it's your boss,
Mr. Kageyama.
Huh?
Hello there, Sir. Okajima
speaking. I'm very sorry.
Now, regarding the loss
of the disc, I can--
Right. There's no need
to worry about that anymore.
As far as I'm concerned,
that disc no longer exists.
[ROCK] I don't understand.
[KAGEYAMA] Given your situation,
I suppose it can't hurt
to tell you the truth.
Keep this to yourself.
It's difficult to explain,
but in order to hedge against
a downturn in business,
our board agreed to aid in the
development of nuclear weapons
for a certain war-torn country.
That disc contained the plans.
It's truly been nothing
but trouble for management.
I mean, nukes in
this day and age.
Really, it makes me
question their judgment.
Anyway, eventually,
I'll be in a position
to do something about this.
But in the meantime, this
cannot be made public, Okajima.
For the sake of the 50,000
employees of Asahi Industries,
disappear into the
South China Sea.
You'll be promoted up
to assistant manager
and I'll also request
that the president
and all of the other board
members attend your funeral.
Well then, the professional
soldiers that we've hired
should be arriving shortly.
[EO CAPTAIN] Is it loaded?
[MAYER] Fully armed, Captain.
Rockets and machine guns.
The more you shoot,
the more the invoice will be.
The Japanese sure are generous.
[EO CAPTAIN] Let's move out!
[siren]
[gagging]
They weren't worried
about ditching you,
though I guess
I can sympathize.
Anyway, there goes the ransom,
which means I don't
get a bonus,
but is all of that really
enough to make you throw up?
Just leave me alone.
[BENNY] Revy,
are you up on deck?
Uh-huh.
I'm picking up something and
it's coming straight at us,
but it's not a boat.
It's way too fast. It's at
three hours five minutes.
Can you see anything?
[REVY] It's a gunship
at minimum altitude.
Damn it! An attack helicopter?!
[MAYER] We have a visual.
I don't need confirmation.
I can smell it.
It's them alright.
Damn them. That's how
they're gonna kill me.
[REVY] Yo, Rock. Heads up.
A gun? I don't want it.
Don't make me hold this!
[REVY] Although, I guess
it won't be much more
than a comfort to you.
[BENNY] He's coming.
He's gonna bite our ass.
This isn't good.
We're in serious shit.
He's firing at us!
Ahh!
I'm pretty sure I know
it's not good, Dutch.
Hit it! Shoot it down!
Shut up!
You think you can do
any better, dipshit?
I hope you realize you're hiding
under a torpedo launcher!
Better make sure
you don't get blown up!
You dumbass!
I've had it with you guys. I'm
getting the hell out of here.
You limp-dick son of a bitch.
You running away?
Stop it. Why do I have
to suffer like this?
I can't take it anymore.
Good. We'll sit back
and watch 'em from up here.
But Captain, we have
the opportunity
to completely destroy them now.
You just don't get it, do you?
Right now, I got
these poor bastards
exactly where I want 'em.
Don't you want to have
a good, long laugh
while they cry, howl, and
piss themselves down there?
Damn it!
You all seem to think you can do
and say anything you want to me.
Everyone. Even my damn boss.
Will someone tell me why the
hell I have to suffer like this?
[ROCK] I'm already dead.
You said it, remember?