[ROCK] There's a
noose that hangs
at the entrance of the city.
It's a message to be read
by all who encounter it.
For the cautious,
the sane, it's a warning.
For the reckless,
the wild at heart,
an invitation
they cannot refuse.
The worst of the criminal
underworld gather here.
They come from around the globe
to butt heads and
jostle for power.
An evil city caught between
the East and the West.
Founded during the Cold War
and nurtured by the
many who came here
to ride the wave of
the illegal drug trade
sweeping across the continent.
The edge of the world.
A crucible of hypocrisy.
A place where people whose
souls have been destroyed
in the relentless search
for money and power reside.
A final stop on
the way to Hell.
How have I managed to
stay alive this long?
With the help of three people--
Dutch, Revy, and Benny.
Also known as
the Lagoon Company.
The name of this
city is spoken of
amongst the
villains of the world.
Many who come here to
make a name for themselves
are swallowed by the
darkness, never to return.
A cruel fate awaits any
half-assed, small-time crook
who accidentally
stumbles into Roanapur.
Right now,
another sacrificial lamb has
wandered too far from home.
The city awaits.
[QUENTIN] Alright then, guys!
Let's get going, shall we?
[chuckling]
Time to get this useless,
cheap-ass job over with!
Okay! Let's head out!
[dogs barking in distance]
[ROCK] So, why are
we sitting here?
What exactly are
we waiting for?
[EDA] By my
calculations, I'd say
one million dollars,
give or take.
[REVY sighs]
[ROCK] Of course that's
what's gonna happen.
I bet it'll just
be another gunfight.
Definitely a gunfight...
Hmph. I'd be grateful
for a showdown right now.
I'll tell you what happened--
this rotten nun's been
blinded by her own greed.
So, who's coming, Eda?
No one's coming, are they?
[EDA] There's no reason
to get all bent outta shape
just because you're bored.
Trust me, this is
gonna be no problem.
Right, Rocky-boy?
But there's gonna
be a gunfight, right?
C'mon, sweetie.
You're a tough guy.
I can't let you die.
We haven't even gotten
to know each other.
Hey, Eda. How 'bout
I crack your jaw for ya?
My, my, look at this.
Never known you to
be the jealous type.
[REVY] Hmph!
Still, I've waited
long enough.
I suppose I can let you
in on what's goin' down
in Roanapur at a place
not far from where we are.
Would you fuck off?!
Now where to begin?
Well, that place
I was referring to
is the lovely Ramsap Inn.
The very same accommodations
I recommended
to that girl who paid
us a visit earlier.
Guess what... Pretty
much any minute now,
a collection of
Roanapur's finest
are gonna come charging
in to the place.
And let me tell you what's
gonna happen when they do...
But the room they raid
will actually be
the one next to hers.
[REVY] And why would something
so convenient happen?
[EDA] Well, that's easy. It'll
happen because I gave them
the room number next to hers.
That stupid woman
will leap outta bed
as soon as she
hears the gunfire,
then she'll most likely
run out to the hallway
to see what's going on.
[REVY] Yeah. Knowing her,
that's probably what she'd do.
Her survival skills are
more or less nonexistent.
[EDA] Exactly. So,
it goes without saying
she won't notice
that her room
is the only one behind
a fireproof wall.
Anyway, the moment
she opens the door,
she'll be facing off
with those dip-shits.
Now if she's lucky,
the hunters won't
have time to figure out
that there's a room
behind that wall either.
And if that's true...
[banging on door]
It's like you gathered together
all the "ifs" in the world
for this lame-ass plan.
Come on, Revy.
Don't be like that.
If she ends up getting
killed, then so be it.
But still, unless the
girl's completely useless,
she'll at least shut
the fireproof door.
It won't do much, but it will
buy her a little time.
A few seconds later, those
guys'll break through the door.
Then they'll all
storm into her room...
...but too bad for them,
it'll be empty.
[REVY] What a joke.
As if things are just gonna fall
into place for you like that.
That's the thing,
I've given her a way out.
If you stretch out on
that bed, even once,
I guarantee you're gonna see it.
You'd have to be blind not to.
Although, there's no way
you'd be able
to appreciate its meaning
until the time comes,
but when it does...
Shit.
Sounds a little
too simple to work.
What kind of person relies
on graffiti for advice?
[REVY] Look up. Look down.
Good for you.
You're a fuckin' jackass.
[EDA] What's wrong with that?
Haven't you heard it's better
to keep things simple?
Anyway, that girl might
be hopeless on her own,
but if she follows
my little game plan,
she'll be throwing for the
touchdown like Brett Favre.
All she really has to do
is follow the signs.
So, how's that sound? Hmm?
Hmph!
Sounds like you need your
fuckin' head examined.
C'mon.
Rock, let's go. Start the car.
Right.
Wait up. Revy, I'm serious!
That room's worked the
last four times outta seven!
[gasping breaths]
--Fuck!
--Hah! See that?!
What'd I tell ya?!
Bingo! Go get her, Rock!
What a surprise!
[JANE] Huh?!
[EDA] Jogging this
late at night?
Very impressive.
You!? You tricked me,
you heartless bitch!
Not very nice.
Also, that's no way to talk
to your guardian angel.
What do you expect?! I thought
I was gonna die back there!
Oh, is that a fact?
Well, whatever.
So, do you want
us to save you?
Think it over carefully.
'Cause if you don't wanna
hand over those plates,
there's not much
I can do for you.
Maybe you'd be better off
running to a mosque next time.
--Your choice.
--Jesus.
How low can you
possibly go, Eda?
Thirty thousand!
Would you look at that.
It's almost bedtime.
Rock, would you take me
back to the church please?
You monster!
A hundred thousand then!
Not a chance!
Hurry, they're after you.
Alright, fine!
Whatever you want, okay?!
Alright. It looks
like we have a deal.
If you... If you
don't actually save me,
I'm gonna come
back to haunt you!
[EDA] Don't worry. If I
took this any further,
I'd start scaring
away customers.
Hey, Eda! Wanna tell me what
the hell you're doing here?!
Hey! What's up?
You guys decide to take
a late-night jog, as well?
We have business
with that woman there!
A useless
one-grand-per-person job!
That's an easy way to make
a little extra pocket change.
Exactly. So, how about it,
Eda? You wanna--
[gunshot]
[HUNTER 1] You fucking bitch!
[EDA] You assholes
make me laugh.
Thousand bucks...
Try a million,
you fuckin' morons.
That's right. From
now on, she's our job.
Unfortunately for you,
we're her recently purchased
getaway driver and bodyguard.
Revy, eat 'em up!
[REVY] Alright!
[RONNY CK] Bring the
cars around! Move it!
Get 'em!
We're gonna hit
the main road!
This is our job, Rock!
Head for the water!
[squealing tires]
[RONNY CK] Damn it!
Looks to me like things getting
very complicated for us.
Complicated ain't
the half of it!
Now it's the bitches from
the Ripoff Church and Lagoon!
This ain't the same as
going after a single amateur.
Deer hunting just
turned into tiger hunting.
Whatcha waiting for?! Get off
your asses and go after 'em!
Cowboy. Situation has change.
Unless you paying us thirty
grand a head, we leave now.
[RUSSELL] What the hell?!
Are you fuckin' kidding me?!
Sure, I heard she's got
two punks on her side now.
But thirty grand for that?!
Y'all such pussies
that you can't handle
a couple of girlies?!
[SHEN HUA] You not in
Florida anymore, cowboy.
This Roanapur.
Understand what I saying?
Our opponents, they
not like punks you know
who get off on making
graffiti on subway wall.
And neither are we,
motherfucker.
We all make living by killing.
You continue
being cheap with us,
you can go after them
alone and see what happen!
Understand what
I telling you?!
Well, you can definitely
talk the talk.
Now let's both of us pray
you can back that up.
But hold on!
The way you're talking,
it sounds to me
like you might know these two.
Of course we know them.
If you from this city,
you would know them, too.
That my point, cowboy!
You better hurry and
call Lobos. Got it?!
You call him and he
tell you the same thing.
[JANE] Where are you taking me?
Is this another trap?
Even if you're trying
to up the price, I don't--
[EDA] If I'd wanted more,
I would've gotten it.
I'm taking you to your
getaway pod as arranged,
so sit back and enjoy
the ride, okay?
Once you're off,
you can say goodbye
to the wonderful world of
Roanapur once and for all.
Well, the sooner the better,
as far as I'm concerned.
Eda, you promised
me cash up front.
[EDA] Yeah, I've got it
here for ya.
[JANE] The ocean...
A port? A boat?!
What kinda boat?
Is it fast?!
I dunno. Why don't you ask
the handsome man in the tie?
Eda.
Anyway, you're gonna
see it in a minute.
And get this--it's a torpedo
boat. So, yeah, it can--
I hate to say it, but
you won't see the boat.
--Huh?
[EDA] No, no!
This isn't happening!
C'mon, this isn't how
it's supposed to go!
The most important part
of the plan isn't even here?!
Fuck!
[whistle]
[DUTCH] Yeah, we're in the
middle of receiving a shipment.
[ROCK] We got a rush job
a little while ago.
You want something to drink?
[EDA] Look at that.
All you've got... is piss.
Although, I can't
help but notice
you've got some
Ardbeg Providence.
I'll take some of that.
What the hell have
you been smoking, Eda?
That's Dutch's. I swear if you
so much as lick that bottle,
I'm gonna beat
the shit outta you
and shove a beer
up your ass.
Fuck you, too.
Will Jim Beam do? We have
plenty of this around.
If that's not good
enough for her majesty,
there's plenty of
toilet water. Fuck.
[DUTCH] Revy, is Eda there, too?
Yeah, she is.
Sorry to cut you
off like that.
That's alright.
Now where the
hell were we?
This job you picked up,
it's getting ugly.
That sound about right?
[BENNY] Okay, we got
everything on board.
Yeah, that's right. Eda's here
and we have weapons.
But we also have two
useless ones to deal with.
Alright, I think
I get the picture.
Just hold on a sec.
I know we just picked it up,
but if we wanna get back
to port as fast as possible,
we should dump this cargo.
Guess we'll have to, but
we'll need some compensation
for breaking the deal.
[REVY] Alright. I'll contact
Isaac about that from this end.
All expenses will be covered
by the Ripoff Church.
Whatever. It won't
be that much.
By the way, where's that girl?
She's unusually quiet.
Yeah, that's true.
She's been in the storage
room ever since we got here.
She hasn't come out once
in the last hour or so.
Space. Scan with box.
TSIG root-authority...
Auto one. One-nine-two.
One-six-eight. DNS?
Uh... Is this it?
[beep]
No good. The port shell's
being booted now.
I can't even get
into my own account.
I don't believe this.
Thanks, Theo. I'm in
really big trouble now
thanks to your precious
programming skills.
[boat horn]
[LOBOS] Dutch, I'm sorry.
What more can I say?
[DUTCH] Okay, Lobos.
We might be from
the same country,
but we sure don't
speak the same language.
These guys don't realize
that they're small fish
in a shark-infested
pond over here.
They just don't get it.
Guess not. When it
comes to criminals,
Roanapur attracts the
very worst of the worst.
Hell, it's definitely
rubbed off on all of us.
A little time with
some real criminals
should teach your
dumbass friends a lesson.
[LOBOS] So, please, give me
just a little bit more time.
[DUTCH] Alright.
Benny-boy. You hear that?
[BENNY] Yeah. Every word.
These guys must have no idea
the kind of demonic energy
they're about to unleash.
Not good. Let's hope
we get there in time.
[DUTCH] I hear ya.
So, Dutch, you know
how you were just saying
that this city has
rubbed off on all of us?
I always thought that Rock
and I were exceptions to that.
[DUTCH] Think again, Benny-boy.
I sensed it all along.
Something lurking deep
down inside the both of you.
[BENNY] Thanks a lot.
[squealing tires]
Damn it!
How long is this gonna take?!
Would y'all
hurry up and... Huh?
Shh!
C'mon now. Just one more try.
TSIG root-authority
and from here, I should be--
[beeping]
[grumbling]
[whirring sound]
[startled gasp]
[EDA] Didn't your mama
teach you to knock first?
Stupid bastards.
[whirring sound]
[REVY] Damn it!
What is up with that?!
Why do they hafta use
our car as a shield?!
Sorry for your loss.
[REVY] Those fuckers! We just
finished having it fixed
after that maid tore it up!
[HUNTER 2] Shit!
This thing's leaking gas!
[explosion]
--Ah!
--Now you've done it.
--Hey, Rock!
--Yeah!
[REVY] Fuck! They're everywhere!
Rock, do you think
you can make it
to the back door
with that girl?
I'll give it a try
as long as you can
hold them where they are.
Not a problem!
Alright, let's go!
--Wait!
--Now!
That's pretty manly of him,
you must be proud!
He's got a long way to go.
[ROCK] This way!
Revy! Help!
What's wrong, Rock?
[JANE] What the hell
are you waiting for?!
Quick! Hurry up
and shoot her!
I would, but I can't!
I don't have a gun!
[JANE] What are you,
stupid or something?!
[ROCK] Yeah.
I was thinking
the same thing.
[REVY] Rock!
Rock! Damn it.
Hey! Revy!
Rock!
[shattering glass]
Damn it! Are you alright?!
Don't have an
answer for ya.
No! Come back! That door
leads down to the dock!
[JANE] You've gotta be kidding!
If I stay up here, I...
[gasp]
It wouldn't matter...
how many lives...
Uh... Uh... Hi.
I have a little
favor to ask you...
Do you think you could
let me squeeze past?
Hmm... Care to join me for a
backyard barbecue, little lady?
Ahh!
Rock!
Rock, get away from her!
[HUNTER 3] Shoot! Shoot 'em all!
[EDA] Revy!
It's those guys
across the street!
We gotta get rid of 'em!
Hey, you! Blondie!
Give her that box!
[EDA] What's this?
You were holding out on me!
We could've used this
an hour ago, bitch!
Yeah, but it's
supposed to be for sale!
I can't see how
that matters now!
You only live once, right?!
[REVY] Damn.
Up here! Hurry!
You too, Revy!
[REVY] Go ahead, Rock!
Shit.
When you stick your head
outside, it's like open season.
It's the same thing
with the front door.
They've got two or three
snipers out there, too.
Huh? What now? Where's
all this smoke coming from?
Ugh. Gimme a break.
That just isn't fair.
I don't believe this.
One of these assholes must've
set fire to the dock exit.
They're really only
giving us one option
and that's to go to the roof.
Bad idea. That'll be
the end of the line.
That is true.
But our enemy should be
worrying about the same thing.
Unless they do something,
that little moneymaker
they're after
is gonna go up in flames
with the rest of us.
Yeah. Right. So, what would
you do if you were them?
[REVY] That's obvious.
I'd force my way in
and take out the guards.
And how are they
gonna time it?
[REVY] Based on their numbers
and the way they're
positioned out there,
we can expect them to spray us
all at once any second now.
When they've got
us pinned down,
they'll storm
the second floor.
But there's no fuckin'
way we're gonna
sit and wait
for that to happen.
Revy!
Is that you, Chinglish?
Ahh, you make good guess!
Who's that? You actually
know this hunter?
[REVY] Yeah.
And believe me,
outta all of them,
she's the last fuckin'
person we wanna deal with.
Yo, Chinglish!
You got your partner
with you out there?!
[SHEN HUA] Oh, Leigharch?
He relax too much
and finally he don't
come back from Mars.
Too bad for him.
But now he living
very happily
with his nurse
at special home.
[REVY] Had to happen
sooner or later!
Eda, listen up.
Say hi for me the next time you
go to visit the crazy bastard!
[SHEN HUA] Okay!
[REVY] She's using
the duct as a foothold.
Okay, but in case
you haven't noticed,
we got bigger
problems right now.
Take a look. That's no fuckin'
campfire downstairs.
[REVY] Damn it.
It's just a matter of time.
This place won't
last much longer.
I hate endurance matches.
I'm gonna hafta draw her out
before she draws us out.
I can get this fox
off that duct
and have her run right
past the front door.
Can you make the shot?
I dunno, Revy,
is the Pope Catholic?
If you can draw her out
and give me a clear shot,
then this fox is
as good as dead.
--[REVY] Let's do this.
--[EDA] Got it.
[REVY] She's headed your way!
[heavy panting]
[JANE] What do we do now?
[ROCK] I'm thinking about it.
It's not like we
can go any higher.
Do you at least
have a plan?
[ROCK] I'm thinking about it!
This was your plan?
How dependable of you.
Let's see... I suppose we could
wait for a golden chariot
to sweep down
and pick us up.
Just shut up.
I'm thinking about it!
[LOTTON] I am here
to take your life!
My name is Wizard!
Lotton the Wizard!