[TAKENAKA] Let me see here...
Where to start? Well,
my name is Takenaka.
Masahiro Takenaka.
Now perhaps you can
tell me your name?
What's the point? Why do you
need to know my name?
It just doesn't seem right
for you to remain nameless.
That's all.
But have it your way.
No big deal. It really
doesn't bother me.
I'll just call you
"brother" instead.
[LEIGHARCH] Hey, baby! I didn't
know you wanted to die so badly!
Volunteering for
suicide, are you?!
Are you from... Tokyo?
[ROCK] Uh... Yeah.
I'm actually from
Adachi, myself.
Do you go to Shinjuku a lot?
Ah, is the Etoire still there?
I love that place.
And how 'bout the
Nichigeki Theate?
Well, I...
I remember after a demonstration
we had at the JNR,
I went there to see Yakuza Cop .
You ever hear of it?
It's a classic!
That was right after
we went head-to-head
with the riot police.
Waltzed right in there
with my helmet on
and my club at my side.
I tell ya, it sure
was good to be young.
Do you miss it?
Do you miss living in Japan?
Let me ask you
something instead.
Why would a guy like you wanna
cross this dangerous bridge?
Well? I doubt it's
for the money.
Not a lot of folks
would choose this life.
These days, Japan's full to
the brim with petite bourgeois.
If you ask me, bro,
the truth is you and I are both
outsiders from that country.
Neither of us really
fit in there anymore.
You know...
...I think I get
where you're coming from
and I guess I'm curious.
I'd like to know why you decided
to take the road less
traveled, if you will.
I'm...
I'm different than you.
I don't wanna be grouped
with people like you.
[TAKENAKA] Oh?
How are we different?
For one, I wasn't chased
out of the country.
But it goes beyond that.
You were forced into a corner
and had to escape.
I'm young, but I know
what you've done.
I've heard all about your
"achievements" in our country.
Bro, you don't know
the half of it.
When I left Japan, it was 'cause
I'd gambled everything I had.
On activism and the concept of
permanent, worldwide revolution.
When you have a will
and a mission,
you concede battles,
but never the fight.
You don't know what
that's like, do ya?
If there's a difference
between us, that's what it is.
I've felt that. I have.
[TAKENAKA] I wonder. A mission
requires tenacity, doesn't it?
And what about you?
You don't have a mission
anymore, do you?
Or even if you do,
you no longer believe in it.
[TAKENAKA] Hey now, brother...
[IBRAHA] Cut it out, Takenaka!
I don't give a shit
about what tactics
you're trying on this guy.
This conversation has nothing
to do with the interrogation!
Alright. Listen up,
you tight-lipped bastard.
I'm not as kind and
understanding as he is.
We don't have time for this.
Where are the documents?!
[REVY] We're gonna
hafta walk from here.
We don't keep driving in car?
I don't wanna charge in
with this piece of shit,
especially with a
crackhead at the wheel.
Fuck you! I'll have you know
this is the world's
greatest off-road vehicle,
you heartless bitch!
This piss-tank's
getting on my last nerve.
Listen up,
you fuckin' leprechaun--
you're gonna wait here
until you get our signal.
If you run away, I'll hunt
you down and castrate you.
--Tch!
--My! She say good things!
I agree very much.
Fuckin' bollocks!
[REVY] Anyway, just go easy
on the weed, okay?
I don't need you all fucked up
when we hafta make a run for it.
You don't worry for this
guy when it come to that.
Even when his brain off to Mars,
he never mess up driving.
Let's go, little miss Chinglish.
You like for me to
split your ass in four?
It is not nice to make fun.
You one rotten bitch!
There's a story.
I heard it a long time ago.
It's about a man
who came to a city.
He went to a street corner.
And all alone,
he began speaking.
[crowd yelling]
Hoping to make the
world a better place,
this man continued to preach to
whoever'd listen, day after day.
At first,
many showed great interest
in what the man had to say.
Some even promised
to fight alongside him.
But then in time,
they all lost interest.
As long as their lives
were comfortable,
it didn't matter to them
what happened to the world.
Still, the man wouldn't stop.
Even as he aged,
with not a single soul
left listening to him,
he continued all the same.
Then one day, a child
who was walking by
stopped and asked
him a question--
"Why do you continue preaching
when there's nobody here?"
And this is how
the man answered--
"In the beginning, I thought
I could change everyone.
Then I realized that
it was a hopeless dream.
But the reason I won't
stop preaching..."
And brother, the reason
I won't stop fighting is...
...back then when I started out,
I gambled my entire
life on this.
If I stop now, all of it
is just one big lie.
Well, well.
Seems that you and I really
are different, after all.
It's a shame.
Takenaka,
how badly d'ya think
we should hurt him?
It won't be necessary. He's not
a soldier, just a delivery boy.
He has no reason to be loyal.
Leave him alone and he'll talk.
And if he still hasn't
talked to us by morning,
well, we are soldiers,
after all.
We'll hold a military tribunal
and send him to
the firing squad.
Tomorrow?!
Every single minute that
passes is hurting us!
We're on the brink
of determining
whether or not
the plan goes ahead.
Why the hell can't
you see that?!
[TAKENAKA] C'mon,
no need to be so uptight.
If we don't get it from him,
then we'll just go after the
girl we left at the village.
Who knows? If we're lucky,
she might just come waltzing
in here to save him, right?
[REVY] Three at the west gate.
Six more at the east gate.
Only a fifty caliber
up front. Any mines?
No mines. Their camp
is very often moving.
Mines are too much trouble.
We hurry now. If idiot partner
talk, this all for nothing.
There's no need to worry.
Rock's a tight-lipped guy.
He wouldn't talk even if they
put him in front
of a firing squad.
Let's move in at sunset.
You ready, Chinglish?
[SHEN HUA] Yes,
twinkie, I ready.
You don't forget,
when we finish job,
I carve some meat off
your ass, stupid whore.
[ROCK] Damn it!
Takenaka!
Oh, you're here.
Sorry, but something's
bothering me.
I received word from
our teams in Thailand!
The other three
cases were decoys!
Which means that your Japanese
friend has the documents!
Your actions are
interfering with the plan
and that is unacceptable!
You...
You know why this
is so important to me
and why we cannot fail.
Tell me...
What ever happened with the
team we sent into the city?
Have we heard from them?
What? Don't change the subject!
What does it matter?!
I'm not changing the subject.
Now how long has it been
since the search party left?
They haven't reported back.
--That's because they--
--And the surveillance team
at the government camp.
That woman hasn't
been found anywhere.
Makes you wonder...
Where is she?
[REVY] What's the problem?
Let me guess--
it feels so good,
you can't pull the trigger?
[SHEN HUA] Men know
much about stabbing,
but no get stab much
themselves. I do for them!
My turn now!
Revy?
Is that you, Revy?
I'm right in here! Revy!
[REVY] Rocky-baby.
You been a good boy?
If you promise to behave
yourself a little bit longer,
sweetie-pie, I'll even
buy you some cotton candy.
So, we're leaving now.
Oh? Is he dumbass
you talking about?
[ROCK] Who the hell is she?
Well isn't this
a pleasant surprise.
Rock! Hurry the fuck up!
Rock, we need a strategy now!
[ROCK] What are you
talking about? Just run!
[REVY] Fuckin' eh!
Works for me! Now let's go!
Whaaat?
I'm actually feeling pretty
good about being right here.
Too fucking bad! It's your
job to drive, asshole!
Now get this shit-heap rolling!
Oh, yeah! I almost forgot!
I've gotta get to Liverpool!
It no use. He very,
very relax now.
[LEIGHARCH] Jimi Hendrix
is calling me back!
He got my message!
He wants me to defeat
the Klingons ASAP!
C-C-Captain Picard!
[REVY] Hey! Whaddya doing?!
You're going the wrong way!
You jackass!
We're right in the middle
of their fuckin' camp!
Goddamn it! Guess
there's no choice now
but to start shooting!
Look at these crazy bastards.
All units! After them!
Pursue that vehicle!
Corner them and make
the kill! Let's move out!
This is reckless, Ibraha.
You can shut your mouth.
[REVY] Seeing as Rock hasn't
snapped under the pressure,
I take it this enemy isn't
all that bad, after all.
[ROCK] No.
[REVY] Look at that. These
fools are coming in droves.
Oh, that is very good.
[IBRAHA] Damn it!
I understand how
you feel, but...
I've been trying to accomplish
this mission for years!
I will not stand aside and let
that gangster ruin it all!
[ROCK] Damn... Damn!
What's with you?
Alright. It's on.
Revy. I talked to that
Japanese guy for a long time
and I realized...
--...that I...
--Rock, paper, scissors!
--[SHEN HUA] Scissor!
--Damn it!
I get fuckin' leftovers.
[SHEN HUA] I see you later.
Hey! You can take out two
of them, then we switch!
Did you say something?
[ROCK] No. Never mind.
I coming for you!
Get ready!
What do you think you're doing?!
Look!
Stupid bitch, didn't I tell
you not to kill them all?!
Move! I'm taking the left side,
you take the right!
No room, get out my face!
[IBRAHA] Let's fan out!
And keep an eye out
for our own! After them!
[LEIGHARCH] Holy shit!
What?
Whoa! Raquel Welch and
Jane Fonda are racing!
How can you not love that?
--Oh. Great.
--[SHEN HUA] You stay down!
--You in my way!
--Get your fuckin' hands off me!
[LEIGHARCH] I don't understand!
Where are you
ladies taking me?!
Could it be? Could it?!
The legendary nude beach?!
[CHANG] Dutch, only thirty
minutes left until the deadline.
Think you'll be able to
sit tight for that long?
Oh, I see.
No, not really. You're free
to use any means necessary.
That's fine with me.
Guess who, Mr. CIA.
Yeah, right on schedule.
Don't worry about it.
Cut it out with the lousy jokes.
And the money?
'Cause I don't take
American Express, you know.
Fine. You let me know
when you get it. Later.
What did Hong Kong say?
Well, sir, they said, "We
permit the bringing of justice,
but the situation
cannot become messy."
Well, I should've known.
So, in other words, they want us
to avoid fighting them head-on.
That's a mighty tall order.
Well, all we can do now is
wish the delivery boys luck.
Okay, we start over then!
Rock, paper, scissor
one more time?
[REVY] We don't have time
for that! They're coming!
[LEIGHARCH] Barbarella's holding
up an anti-war sign in the nude!
[REVY] We've gotta
kill them all!
With this much distance,
your weapons won't work!
My turn!
Have no choice.
Now we see if you any good.
Fuckin' smartass.
This'll make you go cross-eyed.
Damn it!
[REVY] Suck this!
Oh, now I see she not only
good for talking. Impressive.
[REVY] If we had an M-72
or a mini-gun,
it would've been easier
to finish the job.
[SHEN HUA] Stupid. Cannon and
gun, they always needing ammo.
Body and blade last forever.
They always be the best
weapon in the world.
That's the dumbest thing I
ever heard. A knife can chip.
Guns over swords
and nukes over guns.
Now if we had one of those,
it would be the greatest thing
ever. But it's rigged so that
only politicians can
get their hands on 'em.
Fuck!
[SHEN HUA] Your head not right.
It not for you to buy.
Criminal only use such
weapon for making big crime.
[LEIGHARCH] What?!
My application
for the Black Panthers
was denied again?!
[REVY] Gimme a break.
Hey, Rock. You should
have some of this.
It'll calm you down.
Why not?
[IBRAHA] All the base's
vehicles are to pursue them!
It doesn't matter if
you cross the DMZ border!
Drive right through! Find that
jeep and get those documents!
Enough! That's a death sentence!
Give that back!
Ibraha! Don't forget we
have a job to do! Right?!
Ibraha!
Shut up!
No matter what you do
or how hard you fight,
your son is never coming back.
[child crying]
[SHEN HUA] DMZ, yes?! Very soon,
we be seeing the camp.
How ya doin'? You having
fun yet or what, Rock?
Well, how should I put it?
Running away like this
always seems to make
things worse, you know.
Truth is when I
look back at my life,
it feels like I've been
running away from things
since I was in kindergarten.
It's over.
[SHEN HUA] Oh,
it affect him wrong way.
I've never seen him like this.
He's such a positive guy so I
figured he'd just get over it.
No good. Mood important
at time like these.
When I talked to that old guy,
I acted all high and mighty,
but now that I think
about it, that's all I do.
I talk and talk and
then I talk myself
right outta the situation.
Hey! Look at that!
Great. Here we go again!
What is it this time?
[LEIGHARCH] Playmates!
There are exactly one
hundred Playmates, man!
From the '90s! It's an attack
of the Playmate Army!
[SOLDIER] Commander! An unknown
has entered the DMZ!
Permission to fire?!
[COMMAND] Bunker Number Three!
Hold your fire!
To all personnel on duty,
that is not the enemy!
What you and I do, it isn't
just some profession!
It's a way of life
for us, is it not?!
There are times when
we simply cannot give in!
Ibraha.
Those monsters in Jerusalem
and all those who've
helped to protect them...
All of them are finally
within our reach!
And so help me, Takenaka,
I'll show them what the
Red Cross camp in Beirut
was like in '87! That's the
only reason I've come this far!
[SOLDIER] Commander,
your orders?!
Continue with your pursuit!
Find that vehicle!
I don't care if you hafta
--go into the government camp!
--Stop! We must retreat!
Don't be blinded by our ideals!
"Be blinded"? What the fuck
are you talking about?
Isn't that the whole reason
we've been fighting?!
Aren't those ideals the reason
you came to the Beqaa Valley
in the first place?!
Answer me, Takenaka!
[TAKENAKA] To all units--
retreat immediately.
Do not return to camp.
Proceed to the secondary
gathering point.
[SOLDIER] Roger that!
That was our problem. You and I
could only look to the past.
If we keep doing that, nothing
will ever change, will it?
Still...
I suppose none of this
matters anymore,
but you were a good comrade
to me all the same.
What a goddamn waste.
Whatcha got for me?!
Has the launderer's
delivery boy arrived yet?
Well, well. You're
late again, Langley!
[CIA AGENT 1] That's
because Langley's busy!
There's too many bastards
shitting on freedom
and justice these days!
Alright, that's enough
chit-chat for me.
Where's this thing that's
supposed to get us all excited?
Oh, shit! The briefcase!
--Wha...?!
--I don't have the briefcase!
Revy! We're in big trouble!
Don't panic, Rock. If we're
lucky, Aladdin will show up
and rub his magic dick
for us and bam!
Here! Just like that!
What in hell?!
Then why you take us on
long ride to save dumbass?!
[REVY] You guys
wouldn't have come
if I didn't give
you a better reason.
Shit! This thing
is covered in sweat.
Alright, people. Thanks a lot.
Next time, try to keep your
deliveries in better shape,
or the boss'll be pissed!
Oh, yeah, and one
more thing, Rebecca--
if the chief at Buffalo Hill
and your pals
over at the 27th Precinct
happened to hear about you now,
they'd be pissin' their pants!
Damn it.
Now don't get me wrong.
Personally, I couldn't
give a shit.
Our job's to destroy the enemies
of the United States!
They're sure as hell
not paying us enough
to chase criminals, too!
Just a little something
for you to think about
when we call you
for the next job!
[ROCK] Hey, Revy.
I haven't had the chance
to thank you yet.
So, uh... Thanks.
Cut it out. We're buddies.
So, there's no need for this
formal "thank you" bullshit.
By the way, Rock...
Aiyah.
What the fuck
were you thinking?!
Guess what! That's the last
favor you're gonna get from me,
you fuckin' pea brain!
One more thing--
all the rescue expenses
are coming outta your pay!
Next time you wanna be saved,
you better start
asking God for favors!
Gimme a fuckin' break.
[JAPANESE MAN] Oh, hello.
"Mr. Ken." What a coincidence.
Ah! How's life
for the family man?
Was the vacation
worth the travel?
Oh, we really had a
great time. How about you?
Things did not go smoothly.
The trade fell through
and then I ended up
hurting my hip.
On top of that, I left
after having a big fight
with a close friend of mine.
I even tried unsuccessfully to
pass what I couldn't accomplish
on to the next generation.
One unpleasant situation
after another.
I think I must be getting old.
There will always
be a next time.
[TAKENAKA] Of course.
Always a next time.
Till I die, there will
always be a next time.
Oh, before you go, what is it
you do for a living?
My job? Let's see...
Yeah, it's clear to me now.
My job is to be an
enemy of the state.
[ROCK] Vampires?
Those words... They have
something to do with vampires.