(laughter)
[SARASHINA]
Yay, it's summer vacation!
We're gonna go to Maid Latte
every single dayyy!
[SHIROKAWA]
As long as we get our summer
allowance,
we can go whenever we want!
[KUROSAKI]
Our spirit is hotter than
the hottest summer,
and it's screaming that
we'll make this a summer
to never forget!
[TRIO]
Gah!
[SHIROKAWA]
WHYYYYYY?!
[TRIO]
Misaaaa!
[HONOKA]
It's so hot! I can't
take it anymore...!
[SATSUKI]
It's just a little bit further.
Hang in there, Honoka.
Ugh... I never should have
agreed to come on this "company
trip" in the first place!
Come on, don't say that. After
all, Satsuki's younger sister
was kind enough to invite us.
That's right.
No complaining!
Huh? Where'd
Misa run off to?
Over there.
[HONOKA]
Whoa. When'd she
get so far ahead?
Amazing!
[MISAKI]
It's the beach!
[SUZUNA]
I cut the slices extra
big. Wow, how fancy.
Still... Sis went on a
trip to the beach. And
Mom is busy working.
I didn't think I'd win all this
stuff. What should I do if I
can't finish it by myself?
(chomp)
Oh, that's right!
I should call everyone from
the Sweepstakes Club. Ulp.
After I eat this, of course.
(chewing and spitting out seeds)
[NAGISA]
Welcome!
It sure has been
a long time hasn't it, Big Sis?
[SATSUKI] Nagisa! Have
you been doing okay?
[ERIKA] Sh‐She's so tan!
[NAGISA] Yup!
[Misaki] A tan Manager...
[Satsuki] You're the owner of
Beach House! That's awesome!
[NAGISA]
But Sis, you have
your own place, too!
Thanks for coming out, everyone.
You're welcome to rest up before
heading down to the water.
[ALL]
Okay!
[NAGISA]
I'll take your luggage.
Thank you very
much, ma'am.
(gasping & laughing)
[HONOKA]
What a beautiful view!
[SATSUKI]
Oh! This place just
started up this year.
[ERIKA]
Look! There are chairs
on the terrace.
Oh... What a
nice breeze...
[AOI]
Are you stupid?
You girls work at a maid café.
This place is brimming with
harmful UV rays...
Don't you think you should at
least make an effort to take
better care of your skin? Huh?
Aoi?!
[SUBARU, voiceover]
Aoi Hyoudou, 14 years old.
The owner's nephew, who
became popular as Aoi,
the Internet celebrity.
Sex: Male.
Hobby: Dressing in drag.
[MISAKI]
Don't tell me you've
been thrown out again!
[HONOKA]
He's probably just here to prey
on unsuspecting beach goers.
Darn it, Aoi!
You're dressing
like this AGAIN?
Hey, give that back!
[NAGISA] This is
the beach you know.
(AOI growling)
[Nagisa]
The way you dress, I get hot
just looking at you, cut it out!
My older brother dropped him off
here hoping he'd get a little
more manly...
looks like it's had
the opposite effect.
So I can see.
(beach chatter)
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Oh, President.
Why the heck are you
here, too, Usui?
I told you. The manager
asked me to come.
She wanted me
to be the bodyguard.
Gweh!
Even though it's way
too hot outside,
I had to get up early
and came all the way
here. (yawn)
If you didn't feel like doing
it, then why did agree to?
If it's for you, I'll
do anything. You know
that, Misa. Besides...
If you happen to drown out
there, I can't very well let
some other random guy give you
mouth‐to‐mouth, now can I?
(slap)
Well, I'm off to the
beach. Time to swim!
Okay, Usui, we're gonna go
ahead and get changed now.
You really are excited,
aren't you, Misa?
[MISAKI]
Well, actually my mom gave me
some weird speech about
occasionally "acting like a
normal high‐school student"
or something.
It's been a while since I've
done something fun, so I figured
I might as well go all‐out.
You really give your all at
everything you do, don't you?
Uh, Misa? What's with
that bathing suit?
Okay guys, I'm
heading out first!
[MISAKI]
Hey, everyone!
The water feels great!
[GIRLS]
That's her school
bathing suit...
[MISAKI] Aren't
you going to swim?
[SUBARU] Guess
that's no surprise.
[MISAKI] It's the greatest
[SUBARU] Bathing suits are
pretty expensive.
Yeah but does she really have
to wear her swimming cap?
[Honoka] As long as she can swim
and have a good time, who cares?
[Misaki] Come on, everyone!
Yeah, that's Misa
for you, all right.
It looks like she's
really loving the beach.
[ERIKA]
Whoa, some one looks
incredibly dejected...
I bet he was really looking
forward to this.
[SUBARU] Well... at least
he's at the beach.
(USUI muttering to himself)
But he...
[GIRL A]
Hey, are you alone?
You wanna hang out?
[GIRL B]
We don't have enough people to
do beach volleyball. Wanna play
with us?
[SUBARU]
He really isn't interested
in anyone but Misa.
[MISAKI]
How long has it been since
I've been to the beach?
Elementary school? Before that,
when I went gathering shells?
Okay! I'm gonna enjoy this! Uh?
[NAGISA]
That's right. This place is
actually completely in the red.
Yeah, the location
really isn't that great.
It's at the very
end of the beach.
Plus it's the only one
out here on its own.
[NAGISA]
Newcomers here always have
trouble getting the good spots.
[SUBARU]
The place itself is
so clean and new...
Surely there's
something she can do?
[AOI] A crappy place like this
could never get popular!
[GIRLS] Huh?
Hurry up and go bankrupt.
Then I can finally go back home.
[SATSUKI] Aoi!
[GIRLS] He actually looks
like a boy for once!
[NAGISA]
You've got some nerve.
'Specially when you wear
something like this.
Gah! Give that back!
I said you'd get it when you
were done working, didn't I?
(AOI struggling)
But won't you be in trouble
in you don't find some sort
of solution soon?
[AOI] Let go of me!
[NAGISA] Yeah, you're right.
[AOI] Give it back,
give it back...
[NAGISA] If only there was
something that would make up
I might have a chance
at saving the place...
[MISAKI]
In that case... it'd
have to be something
that really jumps out
and grabs your attention.
Something that no one
else on the beach has...
Uh? Guys?
(menacing laughter)
No matter what the
situation we always have...
A secret weapon that
only we can use, right?
(gleam! laughing continues)
Huh? Wait Uh... You
can't be serious! This
is a terrible idea!
Alright then girls:
let's do this thing.
[HONOKA]
Are you ready?
Hello Masters, welcome
to our beach house.
[HONOKA]
Let's walk along the beach
to get the word out.
[SATSUKI]
Does everyone know what to do
if you run into any weirdos?
[ERIKA]
Just politely ignore them.
Hmph. Looks like this calls for
a guest appearance by Aoi. Ah!
[NAGISA]
Hey! Didn't I tell you to go
clean out the shower area?
[MISAKI]
Nagisa!
Are you all right with
them taking over like this?
Sure, why not?
It sounds like fun.
[NAGISA] It'll be a one‐day
event, just for today only.
[MISAKI] Uh...
[NAGISA]
Tomorrow, things will
go back to normal.
If everything goes well they
might be able to grab enough
attention
to keep this place in business.
Besides, they offered their
services for free,
so as far as I'm concerned
they can do whatever they want.
[Nagisa] Call me if
something comes up, okay?
[Aoi] Ow. AH! Hey, let go of me!
Basically... she doesn't care?!
[USUI]
Grumble grumble,
grumble grumble...
For today only, a real, live
maid café is open right here
on this very beach!
Master, My Lady, please
feel free to stop by and
pay us a visit.
I'll be waiting for you
at the beach house.
[GON‐CHAN]
Master, would you and the
Madame like to accompany me?
[SAYU]
We'll have a
limited‐time only menu.
[MISAKI, THINKING]
Is this really okay...?
(fuming) Geez, this sucks!
It's not like anyone even
uses this anyway,
so why do I have to do clean
NOW, when the sun's at the
highest point in the sky!? Oh?
Need a hand there?
How about I help you
out with the cleaning?
What's up with you?
Heh... Well, today...
I was thinking about helping
out from behind the scenes.
Hmph! Did you finally
become aware of your own
utter lack of sexiness?
Your swimsuit is so plain
and boring it's pitiful!
Uh, so I thought I could take
care of the cleaning outside.
You have more stuff you need
to do inside, don't you?
Fine, whatever. Just make sure
you do a good job, got it?
Don't you worry!
Now hurry up or you're
gonna get sunburned.
You shriveled
old raisin! Ahhh!
Raisin?!
Wow, he really
does hate me, huh?
[BOY A]
Is the place you
were talkin' about?
[BOY B]
Yeah, this is it. The
Maid Beach House. Huh?!
Hello there, Masters.
Welcome to the Beach House!
[BOY B]
Uh, hi.
Please feel free to relax
in the shade, my Masters.
[BOY A]
Okay.
Can I interest either one of
you in a refreshing beverage?
Iced coffee for me.
I'll have
an iced tea.
I'll be back with
your drinks shortly.
So this is what a
maid café's like, huh?
I've always wanted to go to one,
but I never thought
there'd be one at a beach
house. Kna' wha'm sayin'.
Good thing we came
to the beach, right?
Right!
Huh?
Uh!
[SUBARU]
My apologies for the wait.
[GON‐CHAN]
Understood, My Lady.
[GIRL A]
She called me "My Lady"!
[GIRL B]
They're so polite here!
Our special, today‐only
"Beach Mini‐cake Set."
My Ladies, would you care
for a free heated shower?
(laughing) Here are your
cold drinks. Please enjoy!
[GON‐CHAN]
Please let me know when you
have decided your order.
[SAYU]
Master, allow me to
show you to your seat.
[SUBARU]
Would you care for a half‐sized
order for the young Master?
It's way too hot.
Ah! Usui!
You were here the whole time?!
That was close! WAY too close!
Misa, what are you wearing?
Well, Manager said...
I'll help out, too! Do you have
another apron I can borrow?
Thanks, Misa... I'm
sorry, this was supposed
to be a vacation.
Think nothing of it! You
always do so much for me.
Well, if you really don't
mind...
Your school swimsuit
kind of sticks out,
So I'll lend you this one, okay?
Uh, yeah...
I couldn't exactly
refuse her.
They've got a lot of customers
right now, so I've got to do
what I can to help out.
Are you saying, you intend to
go out there dressed like that?
Huh? Of course I do. That's why
I changed in the first place.
Why don't you try giving us a
hand instead of lying around?
Look, I've got to get down there
before thing start getting out
of hand.
All the seats are full and the
orders are starting to pile up.
[MISAKI] I better hurry.
[USUI] Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI]
Stop it!
What are you doing?!
(chuckling) So you're
all right, Misa?
With everyone seeing that
huge hickey smack dab in
the middle of your back?
[SATSUKI] Huh?
[SAYU] Thank you for coming.
[ERIKA] My apologies
for the wait.
[SATSUKI] Misa what happened?
I'm sorry, Manager. Please allow
me to wear this outfit instead.
[SATSUKI]
What?
Quit standing there!
You help out, too!
I am helping out,
I'm being your bodyguard.
(SATSUKI giggling)
Thanks for all of your
hard work today. Cheers!
(together)
Great work, everyone!
[NAGISA]
Eat as much as you like.
[MISAKI]
Wow, thank you so much!
[NAGISA]
I should be the one
thanking you guys.
Because of you, this place was
packed for the first time since
it opened!
There were so many people here
it was crazy‐ I don't know how
you do it, Big Sis!
It's all thanks to
my wonderful staff.
(giggling)
[AOI] Hmph.
[SATSUKI]
Here, take this.
They're free tickets
to a hot spring.
A hot spring?
There's one nearby!
it's so close you
can walk there.
Wow.
Let's all go once
we're done eating.
First we go to the beach,
and now a hot spring?
I think this is the best
summer of my entire life!
This side of the coast is
famous for its hot springs.
(MISAKI happily giggles
and HONOKA laughs)
Huh? What's so funny, Honoka?
This area... is actually
famous because it's HAUNTED.
Huh? Did you just say "haunted"?
[HONOKA]
That's right. They say that a
couple made a promise
to throw themselves from
these very cliffs, and die
tragically together.
However, the guy had another
girlfriend, and at the last
minute he pulled back,
leaving the girl to plummet
to her doom, alone.
Her body was never found. A few
months later,
an unsuspecting couple visiting
the area happened upon the exact
same cliff where... they saw it.
[MISAKI]
Saw what? Ulp...
What did they see?
[HONOKA]
Emerging from the dark water,
crawling up the cliff at an
impossible speed...
a woman covered in blood!
(MISAKIs screaming)
Ever since then, all sorts of
ghost sightings and mysterious
encounters
have been reported along
the seashore and in the
surrounding area.
Aah, I wanna
see one, too...
Ulp. Th‐that's just an
urban legend‐ there's no
way any of that's true!
Oh really? Do you know...
why there are so many
sightings in this area?
(laughter)
Because there really
ARE ghosts here.
(MISAKI scared)
Okay, guys! It's
hot spring time!
[ALL] Okay!
(MISAKI still frightened)
I love that it's within
walking distance‐
that's so convenient.
Let's bathe naked so
we can really enjoy it!
[MISAKI]
I agree... GAH!
[MISAKI, thinking]
Naked?! My back! They'll see IT!
(GIRLS squealing)
[MISAKI]
Um... I think I'm
going to have to pass.
[SATSUKI]
Huh? Why, Misa?
[MISAKI]
I'm not feeling too good.
(concerned)
Well... we don't want
to force you...
I'll just stay here and
keep an eye on things.
[SATSUKI]
Well, we'll be back later!
[USUI]
Misa‐?
This is your
fault. Stupid Usui!
If you hadn't put that hickey
on me, I could be out having
fun with everyone else!
Well, why do you think I
stayed behind with you, Misa?
I don't know and I don't care!
If you think that's gonna make
up for your crime you're wrong!
My "crime"? You wanted
to go that badly?
Of course! I hadn't been
on vacation in so long.
I wanted to have as
much fun as I could.
It's not every day you
get to go to a hot spring
for free. Also...
Being with everyone...
helped keep me distracted...
Are you scared...
of ghosts?
No, I'm not! Where'd
you get that idea?!
I just didn't want to waste
those free tickets that the
manager had is all...! Huh?
What the...? Manager! How
could you forget the tickets?!
[MISAKI] Manager! Manager! (sob)
[USUI] So much for the free
coupons. Looks like no one's
going to get to use them
If I start running now,
I should be able to catch them.
Usui! Stay here
and watch the place!
Huh? You're going
to chase them down?
Do you really have to go
to all that trouble just
for some tickets?
[MISAKI]
What are you talking about?
These aren't just any tickets!
They're FREE tickets! They get
you into hot springs that
normally you'd have to pay
money for, but for free!
I can't just let something
like that go to waste.
What if you run
into a ghost?
Uh?! Ulp. That's
not scary at all.
After all, I‐I don't b‐believe
in such r‐ridiculous, childish
things.
Hmm...
That's right there's nothing to
be afraid of! It's not like any
of that stuff actually exists!
Besides, I can't let everyone
waste their money like that
when there's no reason to!
That's just stupid!
[HONOKA]
This area... is actually
famous because it's HAUNTED!
(laughing) There's no way ghosts
are real... I've never even seen
one, not once in my entire life!
There's no way I could believe
in... (heavy breathing)
Uh oh. This is bad. (nervous
laughter) Where exactly am I?
(screaming)
(scared breaths)
(panicked breathing)
What the heck?
It's just you Usui?
I'm sorry... I didn't
mean to scare you.
I locked the beach house up
and thought I'd come with you.
Can you stand?
You really...
are troublesome.
Huh? What?
You're completely
limp, Ayuzawa.
[USUI]
You still scared?
[MISAKI]
You're making fun of me again.
[USUI]
I'm not.
[MISAKI]
You're going to use this against
me later, aren't you?
(USUI chuckling)
[MISAKI] Dammit, let
go of me already.
[USUI]
I won't let go. I'll hold you
until you've calmed down.
[MISAKI]
What does that mean?
Stupid Usui.
What do you think you're doing?!
(MISAKI screaming)
Geez give me a break.
Can't you find somewhere
else to make‐out you two?
No one's making out with anyone!
Yeah, right, like anyone'd be
dumb enough to believe that.
You two are
obviously going out.
No, we're not!
[AOI]
Then why were you two lovebirds
embracing out in the
dark like that?
W‐Well, that's
because...
[AOI] Ugh, now you're
really pissing me off.
You like him, don't
you? Just admit it!
You're wrong! Oh...
[MISAKI]
And so, the first day of Maid
Latte's Beach House vacation
ended with a night that seemed
a little hotter than usual.
[MAN A]
Hot springs sure are nice.
[MAN B]
Yeah, nothin' can beat'em.
(laughing)
Those were just the
extras we didn't use.
Blrgh!
[AOI] Ugh! C'mon, quit it!
[USUI] We're here, so
we might as well go in.
[AOI] I don't wanna go
into the men's bath!
[MISAKI]
So, Usui, did you go into
the hot springs with Aoi?
[USUI]
I tried to drag him in but
then he tickled my underarms.
[MISAKI]
Usui, you idiot!
[USUI]
So he got away.
Did you take a bath?
[MISAKI]
Only for a bit, thanks to you.
[USUI]
Aah, your spiteful
glare is oh‐so‐nice.
[NAGISA]
Good work, everyone. That
was a fun day off, wasn't it?
[SATSUKI]
You said it, Nagisa. Of
course, we can't go to
sleep yet, can we?
Got anything, Subaru?
[SUBARU]
I brought some cards.
And you, Erika?
[ERIKA]
I brought Uno.
What about you, Gon‐chan?
[GON‐CHAN]
A ball game. And you, Sayu?
[SAYU]
A collection of poetry! Honoka?
[HONOKA]
I'll tell SCARYYY stories.