[YUKIMURA]
My name is Shouichirou Yukimura.
And this...
[YUKIMURA]
...is my younger sister, Ruri.
Her dream is to find her prince
charming and marry him to become
a beautiful princess.
(RURI giggles)
Hey, are you even
listening to me, Kanou?
Yeah, you were saying that
someone has been picking on
you again, Yukimura.
[YUKIMURA] Recently things
have just been getting worse
and worse.
[KANOU] With who exactly?
[YUKIMURA] (sigh)
[RURI] You'll never catch me!
[BOY A] Hey, wait up!
[YUKIMURA] Actually, my younger
sis‐ Ah! Ow...
[BOY A] I said wait, Yukimura!
[KANOU] Yukimura?
[GIRL A] We're supposed to be
playing Princess, but this is
just Tag!
[BOY B]
Ruri, wait!
[YUKIMURA]
Ruri!
[RURI]
Huh?
[BOY A]
You know him?
[BOY B]
Who is that?
[YUKIMURA]
Hi there, everyone. I'm Ruri's‐
[RURI]
He's some boy from the
neighborhood.
(YUKIMURA sighs)
[RURI]
Sorry, but I have to
go home now.
[GIRL A]
Aw? But how come?
[BOY B]
What about the Princess Game?
[RURI]
We can play some more tomorrow.
(YUKIMURA dead inside)
[RURI] Bye‐bye. See you later!
[KIDS]
Bye‐bye!
[YUKIMURA]
I'm not "some boy," I'm you're
big brother! (crying)
[RURI]
That's cuz I was playing the
Princess Game.
A princess's big brother has
gotta be more like a prince, or
else it'll ruin the whole game!
[YUKIMURA]
(sobbing) How can you say that?!
[MISAKI]
Huh? What are you doing?
Who's that little girl?
[KANOU]
Um... it would appear she's
Yukimura's younger sister.
(lovestruck)
[MISAKI]
His sister? She's so cute! She
looks just like you, Yukimura!
[RURI] ...rince...
[YUKIMURA] Huh?
[RURI]
You're Ruri's...
Prince charming!
It's settled! I'm gonna marry
this prince and be his bride!
[ALL]
(shocked) Hah?!
[MISAKI] So... she wants to go
on a date with Usui?
[USUI] Lick, lick...
[YUKIMURA]
She begged me all last night.
Are you an idiot?! What kind of
brother would hand his younger
sister to a pervert like this?!
[YUKIMURA] Ehhh?!
[MISAKI] And why are you eating
in the student council room?!
Snacks are prohibited!
[USUI]
What? It's just candy.
You gave it to me yesterday
at Maid Latte, remember‐?
[MISAKI]
No one asked you about that!
In any case, I
absolutely forbid it!
[YUKIMURA]
But Miss President! Last night
...my sister...
called me "awesome" for
the very first time!
(YUKIMURA happy giggles)
[RURI] Big Brother, you're
the best! You're so awesome!
[YUKIMURA]
She said being friends with
a prince like that made me
awesome.
[YUKIMURA] So please...?
[MISAKI] The first time...? Ah?!
[YUKIMURA]
Please, Mr. Usui,
I'm begging you!
Ruri will finally accept me
as her big brother! PLEASE!
You have to!
[YUKIMURA]
I remember when Ruri was little
we spoiled her rotten!
My family's treated her like
a princess since she was born!
Whenever we played together,
she was always the princess and
I was always her prince!
[YUKIMURA]
But now that she's older she
doesn't want me to be her prince
anymore.
[MISAKI]
Well... I'm not sure you can
really do anything about that...
[YUKIMURA]
Don't say that! I have to do
something to win her back!
[USUI]
You spoil her too much.
[YUKIMURA]
I know, but please!
This might help me
regain my honor
not only as a big brother,
but as a man!
[YUKIMURA]
That's why...!
I'M BEGGING YOU!
[MISAKI]
Yukimura... You really...!
[USUI]
I have a bad feeling about this.
[MISAKI]
Yukimura! I had no idea how
strongly you felt!
To think you could get so
emotional for the sake of your
little sister!
[YUKIMURA] Miss President!
[MISAKI] I'm so moved!
[MISAKI]
All right! We'll work our
hardest to get back your status
as older brother!
[YUKIMURA] Thank you
very much, ma'am!
[MISAKI] You hear that Usui?
[MISAKI]
It's all up to you, Prince
Charming! Do your best!
Didn't you just call me a
"pervert" like 5 minutes ago?
[MISAKI]
That's right‐ you want your
sister to rely on you more than
anyone else, right, Yukimura?
[YUKIMURA] Yes, ma'am!
[MISAKI] Okay, then
give it your all!
[YUKIMURA]
Yes, Miss President!
[USUI]
Like I could ever say "no."
[MISAKI'S GHOST]
The day of the date. Wheee...
[YUKIMURA]
Are you sure it's okay for us to
leave her on her own till Mr.
Usui gets here?
[MISAKI]
Just calm down, Yukimura.
We have to try to stay hidden or
else we'll just get in Usui's
way, right?
[YUKIMURA]
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I'm sorry about this, Kanou.
We were supposed to go do
something, but now we're just...
[KANOU] It's fine.
[MISAKI] What were you
two going to do, anyway?
(RURI humming to herself)
[RURI] Prince Takumi!
[MISAKI & KANOU]
"Prince Takumi"?!
[YUKIMURA]
Sorry, she's been calling
him that ever since she
learned his name.
[MISAKI]
Those clothes are so
embarrassing...
[YUKIMURA]
Really? I think he looks like a
real prince!
[MISAKI]
Just who did he borrow
those from?
[AOI] From me of course.
Got a problem with that?
[MISAKI] Aoi?!
[YUKIMURA]
Is this gentleman a friend of
yours, ma'am?
[MISAKI] Uh, yeah, that's right!
[YUKIMURA] Uh?
[MISAKI] What are
you doing here?!
[AOI] I told you I ran into that
guy at the shop yesterday.
[SATSUKI] Eeek! Eeek! What are
you talking about?!
[AOI] He told me he needed a
"costume fit for a prince."
[SATSUKI]
Usui, thanks again for coming in
to work today!
[AOI]
So I had no choice but to make
him the ULTIMATE prince costume!
[AOI]
I even had to sacrifice one of
my days off‐ it was a huge pain,
really.
[MISAKI]
Yeah, you look real broken up
about it...
[RURI]
Yaay!
Prince Takumi! Prince Takumi!
Prince Takumi!
Prince Takumi! Prince Takumi...
(giggles)
[RURI] Uh?
[MISAKI] He face‐palmed her!
[USUI]
What do you wish to do today,
Princess?
[RURI]
Hm... Flowers!
I decree we go where
there's lotsa flowers!
[MISAKI'S GHOST]
"I decree" sure makes her sound
like a princess, huh?
[MISAKI]
He took her to the
botanical gardens?
[AOI]
That guy sure took on one
huge pain in the butt of
an assignment.
[AOI]
Huh?
He's looking over here.
[KANOU]
Did anyone else notice that
there are flowers springing up
out of nowhere?
[YUKIMURA]
Don't worry I saw it, too.
[AOI]
What the heck is he doing?
He's REALLY looking
in this direction.
[MISAKI]
Yeah... he's REALLY looking.
[AOI]
Are you jealous that you're not
the one on a date with him
instead?
[AOI] Jeez, you guys really are
an idiot couple aren't you?
[MISAKI] No, we're not a
couple!
[AOI]
Well, HE obviously wants to be.
[MISAKI]
No, you've got it wrong!
[RURI]
Prince Takumi!
I'm over here! Uh!
[MISAKI] She fell
right on her face!
[KANOU & YUKIMURA] (shocked) Ah!
[YUKIMURA]
Aah! R‐Ruri!
[MISAKI]
Calm down, Yukimura.
[AOI]
Oh, she got up.
[RURI]
(holding back tears)
[MISAKI] Oh no, she looks
like she's gonna cry!
[YUKIMURA] Poor, Ruri!
[RURI]
I‐I'm a princess...
...So I can't cry no
matter what happens
[USUI]
I see.
[ALL] (surprised)
[AOI] Somehow... I didn't expect
him to do that at all.
[RURI] (happy laugh)
[MISAKI] Uh‐huh...
[YUKIMURA]
I bet she'd be happy... if she
had an older brother like that.
[MISAKI]
Yukimura...
[YUKIMURA]
He's cool and strong...
I can't really blame her...
that's the kind of brother
any girl would love to have,
not like me.
[MISAKI]
Yukimura...
[GIRL A]
Look over there! Are they
filming something?
[GIRL B]
That girl looks like
his little sister.
[GIRL A]
She's so lucky to have a big
brother like that!
[MISAKI] Change of plans!
[KANOU] We had a plan?
Listen up! Initially, we
expected things to go
something like this:
[MISAKI]
But... At this rate, if we don't
do something
Usui will steal the title of
"big brother" altogether!
[USUI] (evil laugh)
[YUKIMURA] I knew it!
[MISAKI] Here's what we do!
[KANOU] Is this really
necessary...?
[AOI] What're they trying to
keep a secret for?
[MISAKI] whisper, whisper...
[KANOU]
(thug growl)
Perfect! He looks like a bad guy
(YUKIMURA scared)
straight out of a movie!
Lookin' good, Kanou!
[AOI]
Hmph! Of course he does‐
I'm the one who dressed him.
[MISAKI]
Fantastic! Aoi, you're a genius!
[KANOU]
I can't do something like this‐
it'll never work
[MISAKI]
You'll be fine, Kanou.
I believe in you!
[MISAKI]
Alright‐ here's the plan.
Kanou shows up and picks a
fight.
Ruri's in trouble!
Usui gets scared.
And Yukimura, the true
hero, bravely steps in
to save the day.
[MISAKI]
I call it...
[AOI]
Hurry up and go pick
a fight with him!
[KANOU]
What am I supposed to say?
[MISAKI]
"If ya don't wanna die, do what
I tell ya."
[MISAKI]
Something like that should work.
Usui should recognize it's you
right away,
so just wait for the signal,
and let Yukimura do his thing.
[KANOU]
Hey, you there.
[PEDESTRIANS] (intrigued)
[KANOU] I‐If ya... If...
(nervous)
[RURI] Huh? If?
[KANOU] I can't do it!
[YUKIMURA]
Come back, Kanou!
[MISAKI]
I guess it was too much for him.
[AOI]
In that case,
I have a backup plan.
[MISAKI]
Great! What is it?
And all the maid ladies wear
cute uniforms
with frilly skirts
and white aprons!
[RURI]
The dishes and cups are so
pretty and fancy.
It's just like having a tea
party like a real princess!
[YUKIMURA]
I wonder if Ruri's taking him to
that expensive café she likes so
much...
[AOI]
Sorry for the wait.
[YUKIMURA]
Uh? M‐Miss President?!
Why are you dressed like that?
[KANOU]
Now YOU look like a character
out of a movie.
[AOI] What do you think
I brought this camera for?
[GIRL A] Ohh... They're filming.
[AOI] And I happen to have
just found the perfect
extras for the shoot.
[KANOU] Extras?
[AOI] Oh crap‐ hide!
[SUZUNA] They say it's luckier
to mail entry cards from THIS
mailbox.
[AOI] Phew, that
was way too close.
[YUKIMURA] What was?
[AOI] Hide!
[SATSUKI] This beautiful
weather gets me all happy
inside!
[SATSUKI]
Still, the ennui brought on by
rainy days also has a certain
kind of cuteness, too.
[AOI] There's more!
[SAKURA] Hey what d'you say we
run into that one store again?
[SHIZUKO]
We've been there 3 times in the
last week‐ is there something
you want to buy?
[SAKURA]
No I just like to visit the same
store over and over again‐ it
makes shopping more fun!
[SHIZUKO]
Is that so...
[AOI]
(sigh) Looks like we're safe
now.
[YUKIMURA]
Um, wanna tell us what
that was all about?
[AOI]
Nothing really‐ just trying to
avoid a repeat of last time.
[ICHIROU]
Look everyone,
it's our Master!
[JIROU]
Filming something again?
[SHIROU]
Anything with which we can out?
[MISAKI]
Uh, no, that's all right,
thanks.
[INUYAMA BROTHERS]
Is that so? In that case,
farewell!
[AOI]
So, uh... what was
I saying again?
[YUKIMURA] You were
explaining the new plan.
[KANOU] And about
these "extras."
[AOI] Oh yeah‐ First, we get
out of here and there'll
be a run‐in with our extras,
and then YOU guys will...
[TRIO] Hey, dammit! You
pickin' a fight, pal?
[SHIROKAWA]
We saw a frilly‐frilly Misa!
[SARASHINA]
Frilly‐frilly Misa asked us to
do this PERSONALLY!
[KUROSAKI]
How's this for a scary face?!
[AOI]
Ah! I told them not to come out
too soon!
Those Three Idiots get dumber
every time I see them! So
much for my script!
[MISAKI] So that's the plan. I'm
counting on you.
[TRIO] Aye aye, sir!
[TRIO] Whoa!
[AOI] Hurry, Misakichi,
you've gotta do something!
[MISAKI] Huh?! What do you want
me to do?
[AOI] Usui tossed them aside
like nothing!
[AOI] Now they're going into a
store! Hurry up already,
Misakichi!
[MISAKI] Fine dammit,
[MISAKI]
How cruel, Prince Takumi! I am
your fiancé, but here you are in
the arms of another woman!
[MISAKI]
Why must you always do this to
me, your fiancé?
When you tire of this princess,
you will simply cast her aside,
too, won't you?!
[USUI]
(laugh) That's right. Once I'm
finished, I'll toss her like a
prize I won at an arcade game.
[MISAKI]
What the heck is that?!
Take this more seriously!
[USUI] Huuuuh? Alright, fine.
In that case...
[USUI]
I'm sorry, Princess Misaki. To
think I've been blind to your
love this entire time...!
[USUI] Please forgive me. This
was the only way I could be sure
of your affections.
[MISAKI] Hu‐ Eh!
[AOI] Hey, you're up!
[YUKIMURA] Huh? You‐you mean
it's my turn?
[MISAKI] Hey, Usui!
[USUI] There is no need to
worry. You, Princess Misaki, are
the only one I love.
[YUKIMURA]
That's enough of that!
[RURI] For crying out loud!
[YUKIMURA] Ah?
Why do you always have to get in
the way, stupid brother?!
[YUKIMURA] She found me out!
[RURI] I'm supposed to be a
princess!
[RURI]
I hate you, Big Brother!
[YUKIMURA]
Ruri!
[BUTLER]
Welcome to our shop.
Slow down, young lady!
[MAID] Ah!
[RURI]
Huh?!
(RURI bracing herself)
[BUTLER]
Is everyone all right?
[MISAKI]
I‐I'm so sorry for the
disturbance.
[YUKIMURA]
Ruri! Are you okay?
You're not hurt are you?
Did you hit your head?!
[RURI]
I'm okay...
[YUKIMURA]
Oh thank goodness.
[BUTLER]
Kids these days! Thinking you
can stir up a ruckus in our
shop!
[YUKIMURA]
Ah! Let's go apologize to
them properly. Brother will
go with you.
[RURI] No! I didn't
do anything wrong.
[YUKIMURA] Uh!
[RURI]
You and the all the others were
being mean to me. I was supposed
to be a princess today.
Uh‐huh, that's right. I'm a
princess, so I don't have to
say sorry for anything!
[YUKIMURA]
That's enough, Ruri!
(RURI gasps)
[YUKIMURA]
That's not the kind of thing a
princess is supposed to say, now
is it?
[YUKIMURA]
You'll never find a
prince like that.
[YUKIMURA]
Ruri...
[RURI]
I'm sorry!
I'm sorryyyy!
[MISAKI]
I'm really sorry, Ruri. We
weren't trying to be mean I
promise.
[USUI]
Yeah, you put on a real show
this time didn't you?
[YUKIMURA]
Ruri...
[RURI]
It's okay. Looks
like I'm not ready
to be a princess yet. Besides...
[RURI]
It looks like Prince Takumi
already has a princess of his
own.
[RURI]
Let's go home, Big Brother.
[YUKIMURA] Mm. Ah!
[YUKIMURA]
Today my princess became a
little bit more grown up...
But it seems like she's still
got a long way to go before she
finds a prince of her own.
[AOI] Hmmm... Like I thought,
mounting the camera like this
isn't a enough to get
everything.
[AOI]
Looks like the only way to
capture all of my cuteness is by
getting a cameraman.
[MAN A] Hey, what're you doin'
over here all by yourself,
cutie? That sure is one fancy
dress.
[AOI] Also, someone to do
lighting and throw a few petals
would be great...
[MAN B]
Whoa. She's even cuter up close
and personal.
[MAN A]
Hey, what do you say we all go
have some fun somewh‐
[YUKIMURA] Th‐That's
enough of that!
[AOI] Hm?
[AOI, voiceover]
Aoi Hyoudou, 14 years old.
An Internet idol whose beauty
has no comparison.
[YUKIMURA]
L‐look‐ you're scaring that poor
girl!
[KANOU]
You feel the desperate urge to
go to the toilet‐ hurry up and
get out of here.
[AOI, voiceover]
Appearances aside, Aoi
is actually a boy.
[YUKIMURA]
(sigh) Thank goodness!
They gave up and went away.
[YUKIMURA] Are you all right?
You don't have to be scared
anymore! They sure did run off
in a hurry, didn't they?
[KANOU] I think they went
to the bathroom.
[AOI, thinking]
Who are these wretched
Oh yeah! It's those geeky guys
who were with Misakichi before.
[AOI, thinking]
I wasn't dressed like this
last time. Guess they don't
recognize me.
[AOI]
Say, I have one teensy
favor to ask you... Heh.
[AOI]
Yes, that's perfect. Do an
overhead shot‐ I look prettiest
at that angle!
[YUKIMURA]
But when you say we're doing
a "promotional video"...
what's that?
[AOI]
I'm the famous Internet idol,
Aoi! For someone as famous as
myself a promo is a must!
[YUKIMURA]
Is an Internet celebrity
like a real celebrity?
[KANOU]
No, in reality they're normal
people
who go online and simply claim
to be celebrities. Huh?!
[AOI]
I can hear you, you know!
If you type "pure cuteness" into
any major search engine I rank
first every time!
I've used my perfectly polished
cuteness SPARKLE like a diamond
among rocks! (giggling)
[AOI] Just thinking
about it makes me happy!
[YUKIMURA] That girl's
kind of incredible.
[KANOU]
Indeed.
[SATSUKI]
Oh, I'm so glad I came
to the flea market today!
I've been looking all over
for a new garbage can to go
in the kitchen... and this
was so cheap!
[SUZUNA]
Wow... People sell all sorts
of things at flea markets.
I'm really surprised.
[SAKURA] There!
[SHIZUKO] Uh oh! Take this!
[AOI]
(irritated)
What the heck is this?!
[YUKIMURA]
It's a flea market.
I know it's a flea
market, you moron!
But why are they doing this
crap today of all days?! Huh?
[SUZUNA] Welcome‐ need help?
[SATSUKI] I think I'll just take
a break right over here!
[AOI] And it looks like things
[SAKURA] How fun!
[INUYAMA BROTHERS]
Five of the same, please.
[AOI]
(irritated) I wanted to get
a shot with the river in the
background!
[AOI] I can't do
any filming at all!
[YUKIMURA] "River"?
[KANOU] I think she
[AOI] Ah!
[KANOU & YUKIMURA] Huh?
[TRIO] Uh?
[SARASHINA] Aoi!
[KUROSAKI] What are you
doing here?!
[AOI]
Ugh what are YOU
three doing here?
[KUROSAKI]
Should we tell'em we're trying
to earn money to go to Maid
Latte?
[SARASHINA]
I don't know about saying all
that in front of the vice
president.
[SHIROKAWA]
Why do those guys get to hang
out with Aoi?
[AOI] At this rate, my first DVD
is gonna be completely ruined!
[TRIO] DVD?!
[SHIROKAWA] Isn't
that awesome, Ikkun?
[SARASHINA] It sure is Shiroyan!
[KUROSAKI] Would it be sexy?
[SARASHINA] Shut up,
you stupid pervert!
[SARASHINA]
Hey? How did we end up
holding a camera?
[AOI]
I'd like you to... film EVERY
single part of me, okay?
[TRIO]
(gushing) We'll film it!
We'll definitely film it!
[AOI, thinking]
I'm a genius‐ fanboys like them
couldn't possibly turn me down.
[AOI]
More flower petals!
And there's not enough light!
[SARASHINA]
Okay, now it's perfect! Here
goes, Aoi! Action!
(AOI giggling)
[AOI]
Mmmm...
It's still missing something.
[SHIROKAWA]
Should we use more petals?
[KUROSAKI]
But we don't have
any more petals.
[AOI] Then just go pick them
all up again.
[BOTH] Huh!?
B‐but I stayed up all night
making those flower petals with
my own two hands...!
[SHIROKAWA]
Man is a pitiful creature
indeed, huh, Kurotatsu.
[KUROSAKI]
Actually, WE'RE the ones who are
the pitiful creatures, Shiroyan.
[AOI]
Hey‐ you over there.
Bring me a stuffed animal.
[YUKIMURA] Huh?
[AOI] A stuffed animal‐ and
make it a cute one. You have
something like that, don't you?
[AOI]
Hurry up‐ I want to use it for
my shoot.
[YUKIMURA] Huh? You mean me? I
don't know about that...
my little sister has some
[YUKIMURA] but she'll mad
if I just take them...
[RURI] Big Brother don't touch
these or I'll hate you forever!
[YUKIMURA] What should
I do, Kanou?!
[KANOU] Why don't YOU just be
the stuffed animal instead?
[YUKIMURA] What?! What are you
talking about, Kanou?!
[KANOU] All you'd have to do is
wear a teddy bear costume and it
[TRIO]
One‐two! One‐two! We collected
them all!
[KUROSAKI]
And there's no dog crap either!
[AOI]
I'm sorry for the wait.
I changed into my maid
outfit‐ what do you think?
[KANOU & YUKIMURA] (shocked)
[TRIO] (excited)
[SHIROKAWA] Aoi as a maid?!
[SARASHINA] It's like a
dream come true!
Let's get one thing straight‐
I'm not JUST a "maid".
From now on you'll call me
"MISS Maid"‐ You guys got that!?
[KUROSAKI]
Miss Maid, you say...
That sounds kind of hot.
[SHIROKAWA]
Huh? But wait a sec...
[SARASHINA]
Yeah, sure enough...
[TRIO] "Miss Maid" makes
you think of our‐
[MISAKI]
Masters... would you like some
candy or the whip today?
[AOI]
What the heck are you
freaks imagining?!
You're grossing me out!
[SARASHINA]
Wow! We sure got
some great shots!
[SHIROKAWA]
Why are we picking
these up again?
[KUROSAKI]
We've been seduced by the power
of the maid outfit.
[KANOU]
Yukimura, you seem to be
enjoying yourself.
[YUKIMURA]
Because everyone else seems like
they're having a lot of fun,
too.
[SHIROKAWA]
Okay! Time to take this shoot in
a whole new direction!
[KUROSAKI]
Oh nice! You mean like a
striptease or somethin'?
[SHIROKAWA]
No you dumbass! I mean we have
to give it more action and
adventure!
[AOI]
Hey! What do you
think you're doing‐?!
[SARASHINA] FOOLS! You guys
don't understand Aoi at all!
[SHIROKAWA] Ikkun!
[SARASHINA]
Listen up! Aoi is not simply an
internet idol‐ she is an oasis
for the hearts of all men,
a pure‐hearted fairy whose
innocence is the saving
grace of humanity!
[SARASHINA] She doesn't
need any action!
[KUROSAKI & SHIROKAWA]
What was that?!
[KUROSAKI]
Just because you're a nerd
doesn't mean you have to be a
snob, too!
[SARASHINA] Uh, well I...
[SHIROKAWA] If you don't like
our ideas then why don't you
come up with something!
[SARASHINA]
Well, we could dress Aoi as a
goddess and show her frolicking
with fairies...
[SHIROKAWA] Where the hell are
we supposed to find fairies?
[YUKIMURA] What if someone
cosplayed as one?
[KANOU] Wouldn't it be best if
you were the one who did it?
[YUKIMURA] Huh?
[KUROSAKI] Whoa! Good idea‐
that'd be freaking hilarious!
[SHIROKAWA] It can't be funny,
can it?
[SARASHINA]
I already told you guys that
Aoi's not that kind of idol‐!
[AOI] Heh! (laughing)
[ALL] Huh?
I can't believe you guys are
getting worked up over something
so stupid!
[YUKIMURA]
Miss Aoi... Your expression is
so fresh‐looking!
[AOI] Uh?
[KUROSAKI] Yeah,
it's fresh for sure!
[SHIROKAWA] The
freshest of the fresh!
[SARASHINA] My heart
was a‐flutter!
[AOI]
What are you morons even talking
about?! I'm "cute", not "fresh"!
[YUKIMURA]
But just now you were even cuter
than normal.
When you laughed it was like
your whole face lit up‐ you
looked adorable!
[AOI]
Uh?! Don't be ridiculous. I was
just caught off guard by your
stupidity, that's all!
[ALL] Uh...
[AOI] There's no way that I,
Aoi, could have fun with the
likes of YOU, is there?!
[TRIO] (sobbing)
[YUKIMURA] That's so mean...!
[AOI]
I knew it‐ getting
anything good filmed
is impossible with
a bunch of amateurs.
[AOI]
I graced you with my presence
because I didn't have much of a
choice,
but it looks like it
was a total waste.
[AOI] Ah‐ah!
[YUKIMURA] Miss Aoi!
[SARASHINA]
What the hell's his problem?!
[AOI]
(gasp)
[ALL]
Huh?! Aoi!
[AOI]
(reaching) Aahhh!
[MISAKI]
(relieved) Thank goodness,
I made it just in time.
[MISAKI] Are you all right?
[AOI] (stunned)
[YUKIMURA]
Huh? Miss President?
[MISAKI]
Huh?
[YUKIMURA]
You were chasing after a
purse snatcher?!
[KANOU]
Then the man who
bumped Aoi earlier...
[MISAKI]
Yep, that was him. I got the bag
back to its owner,
but that guy still
managed to get away.
[MISAKI]
Still, it's strange to see all
of you together. What were you
doing?
[YUKIMURA] F‐Filming...
[MISAKI] Oh, so you were
helping Aoi out, right?
[YUKIMURA] Miss President, are
you a friend of Aoi's?
[MISAKI] Uh, yeah, I guess you
could say that.
[YUKIMURA] Good thing Aoi didn't
get hurt, huh, Kanou?
[MISAKI, thinking] Looks like
they haven't noticed who he is.
[KANOU]
Still, to me it appeared that
Aoi attempted to jump forward
herself‐
not because that man
pushed her from behind...
[MISAKI]
But why...?
I know! Maybe she was about to
drop something important to her.
[AOI] Huh? Unh.
[KANOU]
Or maybe she ended up dropping
it anyway or something.
[YUKIMURA] Then we gotta help
her go look for it!
[TRIO] We'll look, too!
[AOI]
You've got it all wrong!
Just forget about it already!
[MISAKI]
Don't be like that, Aoi.
They're just trying to help
you cuz they're worried.
[MISAKI]
If you act like that, your
friends are going to‐
They're not my friends, okay!
Besides they already hate me
anyway!
[ALL] Huh?
[MISAKI] Is that true, you guys?
[ALL] Uh‐un.
[AOI]
How could you NOT hate me!
Especially after I said such
rude things.
[SHIROKAWA]
But when did you
say something rude?
[AOI] I called you annoying and
idiots and creepy, remember?!
[ALL] Oh...
[KUROSAKI]
Hey, that's what we call each
other all the time.
[AOI]
Yeah but it's different
when you're with your
friends, isn't it?!
[SARASHINA] Huh?
It's no big deal.
[SHIROKAWA] Because
we're the type of guys‐
[KUROSAKI]
Who prefer people who don't pull
their punches‐ 'cause that's how
we are.
[KUROSAKI]
'Sides you weren't wrong about
Shiroyan‐ he's an idiot to the
core!
[SHIROKAWA]
And Kurotatsu's creepiness
is second‐to‐none!
[BOTH] Grr...
[SARASHINA] (amused laughter)
Ah, those two are such a
handful.
[SHIROKAWA]
Where do you get off actin' like
you're the only normal one?!
[KUROSAKI]
Yeah, you're WAY creepier,
you friggin' fanboy nerd!
[SARASHINA]
Hey, that really hurt my
feelings, you know!
[TRIO]
(brawling)
[YUKIMURA]
Stop, you guys...
[MISAKI]
Enough!
[SARASHINA]
That felt nice, Misa...
[SHIROKAWA]
It's been so long...
[KUROSAKI]
Yeah, too long...
Well, I can definitely
understand why
you'd call guys like those
annoying and creepy, Aoi.
(AOI giggles)
I can't believe it...
[AOI] (giggles)
[TRIO] (happy)
[YUKIMURA]
Oh! We have to hurry and look
for what she dropped before it
gets dark!
[USUI]
Four gigs...?
[AOI]
I've never met people like this.
[AOI] Guess there's no other
choice. I'll allow you to
become my servants.
[YUKIMURA] Servants?
[KANOU] No thank you.
[SARASHINA] Servants, huh?
[SHIROKAWA] How exciting.
[KUROSAKI] How erotic!
[RURI]
This is Ruri Yukimura.
It's hard to find a prince like
Prince Takumi, isn't it?
[AOI]
I felt sorry for him, so I
dressed your brother up more
like a prince.
[YUKIMURA]
What do you think, Ruri?
[RURI]
Hmm. You look like a weird
prince.
[YUKIMURA]
(sobbing)
[AOI]
Yeah, you do look a lot weirder
than I intended.
[YUKIMURA]
(sobbing)
[AOI]
Anyway, making rice balls
sure is hard...
[USUI] Miss President?
[MISAKI] Ulp!
[USUI]
What are you making?
[MISAKI]
Uh. Don't look! No
peeking, okay!
[SAKURA]
Misaki! It's a bakery delivery!
[MISAKI]
Here come the bread crusts!