[YOUNG MISAKI]
Geez! Why did you say you
didn't want anyone to come?
And now you're all sulky...
The truth is, you wanted
us all to send you off,
didn't you, Yoh?
(sigh) You really are
hopeless, you know that?
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Here. This is for you.
So... don't make that
face anymore, got it!
I want you to take care
of yourself, okay, Yoh!
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Yoh...
Bet you thought it was morning,
but school's already ended.
(chuckling)
[BOY A]
She sure was scary
again today, huh?
[BOY B]
Who, the demon president?
She didn't have to go off like
that just cuz he ate lunch
early.
[BOY A] Even the
teacher got scared.
[MISAKI] Shintani! What are you
already getting into your lunch
It's still first period!
[BOY A]
Hinata, doesn't it scare you
to get yelled at like that?
Huh? Why would it,
it's just Misaki.
Huh?
[MISAKI] Those guys in
the exercise club again?
I've WARNED them about tracking
mud inside the school building.
Crap... Everyone hide!
[BOY A]
Look!
The demon is summoning her
minions...
(sigh) Oh dear, I've worked
up quite a sweat.
[SHINTANI] Oh it's Misaki...
(Boys running in fear)
[BOY B] Let's go! If the demon
catches us, we'll be taken
straight to hell!
[SHINTANI] Misaki!
[BOY B]
Dude, you've gotta tell me:
What the heck do you see in her?
[BOY C]
I've heard rumors she used
to be better before,
but now she's like THAT.
[DEMONIC MISAKI]
Where are the bad boys?
Huh, well now that
you mention it,
I think she used to talk
a little differently...
[SHINTANI] But she's
still as kind as ever!
[MISAKI] I'm confiscating
those bread crusts!
[BOYS]
Like how?!
Well, she always
treats me special!
She's always been nice!
[BOY A]
He's a masochist?
[BOY B]
A total masochist.
[SHINTANI]
But y'know...
Misaki has always
been herself...
[SHINTANI]
I haven't ever changed
how I feel about her.
[BOY A]
Hinata...
Yeah... I've always known I
couldn't have... anyone but her.
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Hey!
[YOUNG SHINTANI] AH!
Whaddya think you're doin'
in those clothes, boy?!
Your gonna get yer
new uniform all dirty!
Jeez!
[GRANDPA]
What's wrong, Hinata?
Why the long face
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Hey! You can't do that, Yoh!
Nothin'.
[GRANDMA]
How was your day
at school, dear?
[SHINTANI]
There's a whole bunch
more people now.
Well I hope you make
yourself lots of friends.
[GRANDPA]
Time sure does fly...
You're already in middle
school, ain't ya?
[GRANDMA]
That's right. You're turnin'
into a splendid young man.
Thanks for the food.
[GRANDMA]
We worried 'bout ya every day
when you first came here.
And you was so chubby, but
you gotten skinnier and
skinnier every day.
That's cuz all you feed
me is vegetables.
Now don't be an idjit, Hinata!
We gave ya meat but
you didn't eat it.
You said you was fine, but
we could tell different.
[GRANDMA]
Thank goodness
you've gotten better.
(embarrassed) Hmmm...
(Baseball getting hit)
(Girls cheering)
[UMPIRE]
Safe!
[SHINTANI] Phew!
[BOY A]
You sure have gotten fast, huh?
Even though ya still don't have
any meat on your bones.
But I been workin' out 24‐7...
(Girls squealing and
cheering for Shintani)
[BOY B]
Golly Hinata, you sure are
popular with the ladies...
[BOY A]
That's cuz he's the star player,
he gets all the ladies.
[BOY C]
Dangit! Even though he's such
an idiot?! I'm so jealous!
[SHINTANI]
But I... I just don't...
(surprised gasp)
[SHINTANI]
That's right...
Today's Valentine's Day.
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Here. This is for you.
Take care of
yourself, okay, Yoh!
(exhale)
[SHINTANI]
Okay, right this way please!
[MISAKI] Huh?
A Yumemishi concert?
Yup! They'll be playing at
the Yumesaki High School's
cultural festival!
Have you forgotten about how
that jerk treated you the last
time we saw him?!
That's exactly right.
Please talk some sense
into her, Misaki.
But Kuuga's changed a lot
since the last time you saw
him...! He really has...
[SHIZUKO]
Apparently, he got hurt during
what Sakura intended to be her
final concert,
and this "change" occurred
when she constantly visited
him in the hospital.
[MISAKI] Hey, dammit!
[SHIZUKO] Dammit...
[MISAKI, SHIZUKO]
Dammit, Dammit!
[SAKURA]
I'm sorry! But... But I...
I only wanted you guys to see
with your own eyes
how much he has really
changed, afterall!
Uh... All right, fine.
[USUI] I want to go, too.
[MISAKI] Huh?! Usui!
I want to go to Yumesaki's
cultural festival, too.
What do YOU want to come for?
[SAKURA]
Aw c'mon, Misaki!
[SHIZUKO]
You can't leave him all
alone, can you Misaki?
He's not some little kid...
Misaki, your face is quite red.
[SAKURA]
You're all warm, too!
[MAIDS]
Welcome back, Masters.
[ERIKA]
Eriiii‐calyyyy... Eri‐calypso!
Please, have a seat.
[TRIO]
Okay!
Miss Erika, tell me my future!
Will Misa and I‐
Misa and I‐!
Become involved?!
Very well.
I shall now look
into the globe and
predict your futures with Misa!
[ERIKA] Pasahr... Rusoraono...
[ERIKA] Eriiii‐carbornara!
[TRIO] Nervous... So nervous...
[SATSUKI] Hmm. After the shrine
maiden fortune‐telling event
went over so well.
I thought the crystal ball
would be perfect.
But Manager, take a look:
although her technique is
strange she has them completely
captivated.
[SUBARU] They're
practically spellbound.
[SAYU] [GON‐CHAN] Viva, viva,
hey! Viva, viva, hey!
[ERIKA]
Bravo! Eri‐caly, come on!
(Chanting continues)
[TRIO]
So nervous...
[ERIKA]
There it is! It's...!
What is it?
My heart's racing!
I'm stimulated beyond belief!
(Erika lets out
a cry of despair)
(Trio startled)
Hmmm, I see nothing‐
my crystal is blank like
the mind of a simpleton.
[SHIROKAWA] Huh?
[SARASHINA] What does that mean?
[KUROSAKI]
Is it broken or something?
I see nothing! Nothing at all!
In other words... Gentlemen.
You have no future whatsoever!
It means "It will never
work out between you,
so just give up now."
So sayeth the all‐knowingest
crystal ball.
[TRIO]
You didn't have to be
so blunt about it!
Telling fortunes requires
a certain level of human
observation.
So it would be impossible
for someone like you, Misa.
[MISAKI] Huh?
(forced laugh) I mean,
you can't even figure your OWN
feelings out, can you?
[BOTH]
Hello, welcome back, Master!
Hey Misaki‐ Oops! I forgot
that she's "Misa" here.
But just calling her "Misa"
is so embarrassing! (giggling)
[MISAKI]
Shintani... You've already
turned into a regular customer.
Oh yeah! It said there was
"Fortune‐Telling" out front.
Can I get my fortune told, too?
[MISAKI]
Oh, of course, Master.
Now then, Master, would you
please have a seat in front of
the all‐knowing crystal ball.
[SHINTANI]
This is just like
the real thing!
[SHINTANI]
Can you tell me my
future with Misa?
[ERIKA]
Are you ready?
Bashar... rusoraono,
Eri‐cardamom!
(Noise deflating)
[ERIKA]
I saw it.
What did you see?!
A paper boat...
[SHINTANI]
A paper boat and‐?
...it was sinking.
[SHINTANI]
Huh?!
[KUROSAKI] What a loser.
[SHIROKAWA] Didja hear that‐
His relationship with Misa
is a sinking paper boat.
[SARASHINA] Not having a future
with her is better than that!
L‐Look again! There's not a hole
in it or anything, right? C'mon
just look one more time!
[KUROSAKI] What's this?
[SARASHINA] Looks like
someone's in denial.
(laughter)
[ERIKA]
Uhm, well, I didn't
see a hole...
Thank goodness!
As long as there's not a hole,
it can pop right back up!
[TRIO]
So positive!
[ERIKA] Bonus!
[SHINTANI] Oh?
If you can keep your positivity
you may be able to bring
the paper boat back to the
surface of the waters of love...
You might just be able
to change your fortune.
You really mean it?!
Yahoo!
[USUI]
(sigh) In that case... would
you mind telling MY future
with Misa, too?
[MISAKI] Gahah!
(Dogs growling)
[SATSUKI]
Is it just my imagination
or are there dogs in here?
Very well. I shall now
tell your fortune.
Tota eusoraono,
Eh‐ri‐chamomiiiiile!
(chanting noises) HA!
[ERIKA]
Hmph... uhhhh...
[MISAKI]
She's totally avoiding
eye contact!
[USUI]
What does the reading say?
Uh, well... Um, it, uh... heh...
[USUI]
Please be totally honest.
I see. Very well...
For you two, there is...
no future at all!
[BOTH]
Shock...
[ERIKA]
The crystal ball sees fire and
water. You two have the worst of
compatibility.
[ERIKA]
Neither one of you can accept
the other!
[SHINTANI] Hmm?
However, if you wish to continue
being with each other,
you will have to attempt the
great challenge that awaits.
Or else your future is
doomed for certain failure.
[KUROSAKI]
Huh? But she didn't have
anything to say about US?
[SHIROKAWA]
Can't she do some kind of
follow‐up or something?
[SARASHINA]
Please, Oh wise Erika!
[TRIO]
We should probably get outta
here.
We'll just be on our way...
Don't mind us!
[MISAKI]
See you tomorrow.
[SATSUKI]
Oh, bye, Misa‐ good work today!
[MISAKI]
Uh? You waited for me?
That bottomless pit Sanshita was
hanging around for a while, too.
But he finally left.
[MISAKI]
Huh...
That bother you?
[MISAKI]
Why should it?!
There may be some unexpected
"turn of events" awaiting you,
Ayuzawa.
That is if Mr. Sanshita hits
a winning homerun from behind.
[MISAKI] Hey!
[USUI] I see.
Our compatibility was just
that terrible, was it?
Wait a minute, Usui! Don't tell
me you actually believe any of
that fortune‐telling crap!
[USUI]
Is that why you're so cold
towards me, Misa?
No, that's because you're
a perverted freak.
[USUI]
It must be our COMPATIBILITY
that makes you say that.
Are you some kind of idiot?
[USUI]
Fire and water can never be
together...
What, so you're saying you plan
to give up on me
over something
stupid like this?
[MISAKI] Uh...
[MISAKI]
Uh, th‐that is... I mean...
I swear, the next time
I see those guys
they're gonna wish they'd
never exercised in their life!
[SHINTANI] Oh?
What, so you're saying you
plan to give up on me
over something stupid like this?
[SHINTANI]
Let me give you a hand,
Misaki, whaddya say?!
Shintani...
This floor sure is a mess, huh?
Yoh, you have to help with
the cleaning, too!
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
I am!
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Geez! You're such a bad liar!
(Misaki giggles)
Uh? I‐is something wrong?
[MISAKI]
No. You've just really...
Thank you. You're
a big help, Shintani.
O‐Oh really?! I'm g‐g‐glad!
I'll do my best! My total
best! My best!
[MISAKI]
Shintani? What's with you?
N‐N‐N‐Nothing at all!
I'll go get some more water!
What, already?
[SHINTANI]
Ah... She was just so cute I
thought I was gonna die! Huh?
[SHINTANI]
Misaki! Misaki!
Wouldn't it be faster
if we use this?
Oh, the hose? I wonder if it
will reach from over there.
[SHINTANI]
Well, if you push down on the
end like this...!
[MISAKI] Oh...
[SHINTANI]
Waaaaugh!
Idiot! Didn't you put on
the hose securely first?
It's freezing! Why are you
plugging it with your hand?!
Just turn the faucet off!
Uh... Which way does
it turn again?
(angry) Look, just move! Quit
trying to plug it with your
hands, stupid!
[SHINTANI]
Uh... I‐I'm sorry, Misaki...!
What are you doing? Isn't it
a little cold to take a swim.
[MISAKI]
Usui, you again?
You should change
before you catch a cold.
But if you really want to play
in the water that bad, I won't
stop you.
[MISAKI]
Shut up. Hey, Shintani, do you
have any spare clothes?
[SHINTANI]
oh yeah, I have a pullover.
Hurry up and change and then
head straight home, okay?
[SHINTANI]
What about you Misaki?
[MISAKI]
I'll go to the nurse's office
and figure something out.
Later‐ You hurry up and go, too.
[USUI]
(sigh) Just a moment, President.
[MISAKI]
Huh?
[USUI]
You plan to walk
around like that?
Yeah. I'm going to
go around outside
so I don't get any water
in the halls.
[USUI]
That's not what I meant.
Uh... What's the big deal?
It's not like my underwear
is showing.
[USUI]
Hmm. What do you think, blushing
man over there?
[SHINTANI]
Gah!
What are you blushing
like a schoolgirl for?
You really shouldn't be so
careless, Miss President.
It's dangerous.
[MISAKI]
Look, this isn't necessary!
[USUI] If you don't wear this,
I'll walk around naked.
[MISAKI] What?!
[USUI]
So you don't mind if I get
naked and dance in front of
the entire school?
[MISAKI]
Ah! Okay, fine, just don't
strip! You pervert!
[MISAKI]
Fine, I'm going, I'm going!
[USUI]
Woof!
[SHINTANI] Hrm?
[MISAKI]
What did you say "woof" for?
[USUI]
I just felt like it.
Now you try saying "meow."
[MISAKI]
Wha? What is wrong with you?
(Struggled grunts)
Woof!
[SHINTANI]
A boyfriend?
[BOY A]
Yeah. Don't ya think
she's got one already?
[BOY B]
Especially if she's as much of
total cutie like you say she is.
[BOY A]
Maybe she's gotten all fat and
ugly‐ then you'd have nothin' to
worry about!
[SHINTANI]
Misaki would be cute
even if she got fat!
[BOY A]
Then I bet she's definitely
got a boyfriend.
[BOY A]
You haven't thought
about that already?
Don't be stupid, man.
We're almost in high school.
[BOY B]
Y'know them city girls,
even in middle school...
[BOY A]
But especially in high
school, they go for a
little this and that...
[SHINTANI]
What? A little what?!
[BOY C]
What're you lookin' so
traumatized for?
[BOY A]
You should see the little black
book I found in my old sis's
room.
She plays around with guys
and juggles'em like you
wouldn't believe.
[SHINTANI]
Misaki would never do that kinda
thing, she's still pure,
she's not like those
other girls at all!
[BOY C]
Look, just lay off the
middle‐schooler and let
him have his dream!
[BOY A]
But don't you think it's 'bout
time he grew up and faced the
cold hard facts of life?
[BOY C]
True, I do worry about
him not facin' reality.
'Specially since he won't let go
of the candy wrapper he got from
her when they said goodbye.
[SHINTANI] How do
you know that?!
[BOY C] You know what he did?
He took the matching good luck
charm we baseball club members
got,
opened it, and put that
wrapper inside instead.
[BOYS] What?!
[BOY A]
So you're why we lost those two
summer games?! Dangit, Hinata!
[SHINTANI]
You idiot, this is why we got
to the finals!
[BOY B]
You suck!
[BOY C] In the end,
that doesn't matter...
[Boy C] Hinata.
[SHINTANI] Huh?
I know you've got your heart
set on going to high school
with her, but...
If you keep your hopes too high
you could lose your place to
fall back on.
[BOY C] If you're prepared
for that, then go.
[SHINTANI]
I thought I was prepared but...
It sure is rough.
[SHINTANI]
I'd rather have Misaki get mad
at me for not knowin' when to
quit...
Then give up on her
without tryin' at all.
[MISAKI'S GHOST]
A few days later, the weather is
quite goo‐‐ Whoa, look out!
[YUKIMURA]
Hey, Kanou!
Were you waiting long?
[KANOU]
No, I wasn't waiting too long.
[YUKIMURA]
I heard that Yumesaki's school
festival
is supposed to be incredible.
[KANOU]
Indeed.
[AOI] Huh?
[KANOU] Huh?
[YUKIMURA]
AOI!
[AOI]
Perfect timing.
I came to take that shot of me
in front of the water
that I couldn't do last time.
[AOI]
You two are free, right? Here,
hold this, huh.
[YUKIMURA]
You got us again, huh?
[KANOU] So we ARE doing it?
(Fireworks exploding)
[AOI]
The fireworks are way too loud,
so we'll save the best
stuff for later, okay?
(Chuckles)
[SAKURA]
Whoa, this is amazing!
[MISAKI]
I'd heard the rumors, but seeing
is really believing...
[SAKURA]
It sure looks like their
school likes festivals!
[SHIZUKO]
Apparently they begin
preparations 6 months in
advance.
(Girls screaming)
[MISAKI, SAKURA] Huh?
What's everyone screaming about?
Could it really be them...?!
(Squealing)
[MISAKI]
Yumemishi. There they
are. Sakura, she's gone!
[SAKURA] Hey, Kuuga, I brought
you some delicious snacks!
[GIRL A] Hey, I saw him first!
[MISAKI]
Sakura!
[KUUGA]
What did we say? If you want us
to love you, you have to promise
to be good girls. Alright, then.
[KUUGA]
Any nice kitties that can keep a
promise‐ follow us.
(GIRLS squealing excitedly)
[MISAKI]
Sakura! Shizuko! Aaaahhhh!
[MISAKI] You got pulled
to the front of the stage?
So then you're...
[USUI]
They're somewhere in front of
this endless wall of people.
[MISAKI]
Whoa...
[SHIZUKO] This line is to get
spots for their show,
[SAKURA] No! No! No!
[SHIZUKO] and Sakura is refusing
to move even a single step back.
[SAKURA]
No! I can't get farther away
than this or my life will be
over! (extended crying)
[SHIZUKO]
(sigh) It looks like we're
trapped here, at least until the
show is over.
I'm sorry, but I don't think
it's possible for us to regroup
at the moment.
[SHIZUKO]
You two have fun on your own for
a bit.
Huh?! But Shizuko!
[SHIZUKO] We'll talk again soon.
(Phone disconnecting)
She said "have fun,"
but still...!
[GIRL B]
Hey, hey. Kuuga's been different
recently, hasn't he?
[GIRL C]
The members have a totally
different vibe to them.
[GIRL B]
Like they're trying so hard, in
a good way.
I think there's a
different level of respect
between them and the fans...
[GIRL D]
And I've stopped hearing rumors
of them hanging all over their
fans like they used to.
As a fan who just wants to
hear their music, that makes
me happy.
[MISAKI, thinking]
Sounds like that Kuuga guy
really has changed, just like
Sakura said.
Whether or not I trust him is a
different story, though...
[MISAKI] I'm worried about
Sakura... Worried, but...
(Misaki sighing)
[MISAKI]
How we see things and how we
think is totally different...
[MISAKI]
But, but still... (groan)
No matter how hard you
think about it, some
things can't be changed.
For now, let's just
have some fun.
[MISAKI]
H‐Have fun? Have fun how?!
I feel like you're still just
leading me around.
[USUI]
Anyway, let's just have fun.
[MISAKI]
No thank you! You always say
things like that!
[USUI]
C'mon, let's at least enjoy
Yumesaki's festival together.
[MISAKI]
Now you're acting like a spoiled
kid? What a pain.
[MISAKI]
Let's go find Shizuko and
Sakura.
[SHIZUKO]
Huh? Isn't Kamumushi's show
starting yet, Sakura?!
[SAKURA]
It's YUMEMISHI! I sure
hope Kuuga sings a new song!
[USUI] Speaking of, President,
shouldn't we at least mention
that the next episode is the
last one?
[MISAKI]
Oh, you're right. I guess we
should do something
appropriate...
[USUI]
Yeah, that's just like you.
[MISAKI]
Usui, you idiot!