Quit your whining already!
[MISAKI]
Yukimura, I told you the
deadline for the report
on the school festival
was today, didn't I?
Yes! But Miss President
this is a tremendous
amount of paperwork!
Almost all of the
clubs and classes
turned in their paperwork
at the very last second!
Huh?! There's MORE?!
I can't do it!
[MISAKI]
All right, fine!
Just collect everything,
and I'll do it myself later.
Really?!
[BOYS]
Oh yeah, check THIS out!
Show me some more!
Oh yeah!
I can't take it!
(Grunt)
[MISAKI]
What's that sound?
What's going on
over there?
Huh? Uh...
(Boys chatter)
Shh...
(Boys excited)
Shh!
Whoa! Wow!
Those idiots, who have no
concern for their own lives,
wouldn't happen to be looking at
something innappropriate
while I'm away, would they?
Make sure to tell them this:
"Prepare to be punished."
[USUI]
That won't do, Madam President.
"Prepare to be punished"?
Sounds a little suggestive.
They might get the wrong idea.
When did you get here?!
And don't just barge into
the dressing room like that!
A certain someone left
the door open. How careless.
Why you...
Oh, my! Back again
so soon, Usui?
What's in the
box, ma'am?
Oh, nothing!
Just a few essentials...
[MISAKI]
Personal protection items?
What? You mean you haven't
heard about the stalkers
who've been going after girls
who work at cosplay cafes?
Seems like it keeps happening
more and more, so I picked
these up just in case.
Well, I'm sure none of
our customers would do
anything like that,
but make sure to carry one
just in case, okay, Misa?
Here.
Uh, you can just give it
to one of the other girls.
I'll take whatever's left.
In fact, I really don't
need one at all‐
You think you don't
need one because you're
strong or something?
[Grunt]
Oh, that's right!
You know how to do
aikido, don't you?
Right. Besides, I doubt anyone
would try and wait around
for me to leave.
And even if they did,
I'd just take them out!
(giggle)
[SATSUKI]
You sure are tough, Misa!
(giggle)
[KUROSAKI]
Oh. The stalking incidents, huh?
[SARASHINA]
They've been targeting
cosplay coffee shops, right?
I saw it on the news.
What a bunch of losers.
Don't they have
anything else to do?
Do you think
Misa'll be all right?
I dunno...
[ALL]
Ah! I'm so worried!
What if something
happens to Misa?!
All right. That just means WE'LL
have to protect her, right?
But Misa's already
really tough!
And she knows aikido!
She's way tougher than we are!
She'll be JUST FINE!
Well then, shall we
stop by today?
Maid Latte
here we come!
I can't wait to
see our Misa!
Ah!
Waah!
President, please
go easy on them...
Are these all of the idiots
who were making a scene in
the student council room?!
Yes.
President... have mercy...
Next time you want to hang
around in the student council
room looking at dirty pictures,
just go home and study instead!
[BOYS]
Yes ma'am...
[USUI]
Good work.
Staaare.
What're you doing over there?!
Bleh!
What the hell is his problem?!
Is he trying to piss me off?!
[MISAKI]
Fine, just do whatever the
hell you want! Stupid Usui!
(Misaki roars)
[ALL]
Yayyy! Class is finished!
Yahoo!
[SHIROKAWA]
Ikkun, Ikkun,
how much ya got?
[SARASHINA]
20 yen. How 'bout
you, Shiroyan?
80 yen. How 'bout
you, Kurotatsu?
[KUROSAKI]
I've got
15 whole yen!
So, how much would
we have if we added
it all together?
Let's see...
about 115 yen, right?
Huh? We can't
even get a cup of
coffee with that!
[SHIROKAWA]
Guess we'll just give up
and go home.
[Others]
Boo...
(Straining)
Mission accomplished!
Ma'am! Thank you very much!
No problem.
Good work, Yukimura.
(Sigh)
Geez, it sure is late.
(Creepy giggling)
Huh?
[GIRL]
Oh really...?
Let's do it like this...
(Creepy giggling)
Huh?
(Cute giggling)
Aah, I'm really getting ahead!
Sakura?!
Huh? Misaki!
You stayed late, too?
Yay, come study with me!
[MISAKI]
Huh? You were doing your
homework at school? Why?
It's way easier for me
to concentrate there!
It's not safe for you to be
out alone this late at night.
You never know what kind of
weirdos are hanging around.
Yes, Ma'am.
Misaki, you're just like my mom.
Thanks for seeing me off!
She really needs to be
more careful...
It's not safe for
you to be out alone
this late at night.
You never know what
kind of weirdos
are hanging around.
Phwoo.
GAH!
Cut it out, dammit!
You going to work now?
Don't follow me!
(Doorbell)
Welcome back to Maid Latte!
Hello, I'm back!
Please follow me
right this way, Master.
Yes ma'am!
Staaare...
(Groan)
Just ignore him!
Huh?
Oh, allow me to
get you another one.
You're so sweet, Misa.
Thank you.
Hmm...
Later, guys!
Have a good night.
The boss sure is
late isn't she?
She's stuck at one of her
Mall Committee meetings.
They always run long.
Hm... but why today
of all days?
What's wrong?
Do you have something
you need to do, Erika?
I have a ton of assignments,
and they're ALL due tomorrow!
Ugh, I don't think
I can do it...!
Huh? Don't you
have to leave, too?
Yeah. I have another
shift at my second job
at the cabaret.
No way!
You work too hard!
Don't worry about it.
Huh?
The two of you just go ahead
and leave if you need to.
I'll stay and cover for you
until the boss gets back.
You sure, you really don't mind?
I'll be fine!
Just leave it to me.
Thanks for helping
us out, Misa.
But I'm a bit worried
about leaving you
here all alone.
Especially with all of
those incidents that've
happened recently...
Yeah.
Don't worry you two.
Even if some weirdo
does show up,
I'll make him wish he'd
picked another café!
You'll really be okay?
Yep!
Well, if you
really don't mind...
We owe you one!
Now to make sure everything's
properly locked up...
(Locking door)
(Muffled struggling)
This is the weirdo
the boss mentioned!
And he's pretty strong, too!
(Muffled struggling)
What the hell are
you doing, Usui?
I'm playin' stalker.
Well guess what, Mr. Stalker,
playtime's about to be over...
Is this the end?
(exasperated sigh)
Seriously, Usui?
Quit messing around‐ any normal
girl would've sued you for that.
I'll keep that in mind.
By the way, the back
door was unlocked.
Miss President, you need to be a
bit more cautious in the future.
Huh?
You're at ease
because you're tough,
but you should remember...
You are still a girl, after all.
Uh?
Let go!
Why do you always take
your jokes too far?
And who do you think you are,
giving me warnings?
I don't need you
to tell me what to do!
Just leave.
Hm.
See ya.
That girl... she just
doesn't get it, does she?
[SUZUNA]
Wow. So many fancy cakes...
Weren't these expensive?
Did you go on a cake
spending spree? I approve!
No, I kept an eye on the store
today while the manager was out.
When she came back,
she brought these and said:
I'm sorry I was gone so long!
Please take these
and enjoy them.
And now they're ours!
Hmm...
That damn Usui‐ why doesn't he
just mind his own business?
I can take care of myself!
But, I guess complaining
about it won't solve
anything, now will it?
This one's for Mom.
This one is for
breakfast tomorrow.
Oh! This cake tastes amazing!
I wonder where the boss
bought them?
This one's for a snack...
But I can't decide which
one to eat right now.
Suzuna, you can have
whichever one you want.
They're delicious!
We should make some tea
to go with it, too!
Good idea.
We have a "Mysterious
Teas of the World" set
that I won
in a giveaway.
Yeah, that sounds great!
(School bell)
[BOY]
So, you wanna go somewhere
on the way back?
[OTHER BOY]
Sorry, I can't.
I'm broke.
I hear that.
[MISAKI]
See you next time, Master.
Have you decided on
your order, Masters?
Uh, I'd like a Cutesy Cutesy
Omelette and and iced coffee.
[HONOKA]
Right away.
One Cutesy Cutesy Omelette...
[MISAKI]
It's so peaceful.
Without Usui around,
everything seems so relaxed.
(Glass breaks)
[Customer]
Oh!
I‐I'm sorry!
I hit it with
my arm...
Oh, I'm very sorry.
Are you injured, Master?
N‐no ma'am.
I will return shortly with
something to wipe this up.
Wait, let me‐
Huh?
It's dangerous.
O‐okay.
Sure enough, Misa's the
perfect choice, isn't she?
I don't think I can
hold back anymore.
Me either.
[NEWSCASTER]
Last night, a young woman
was assaulted at a
local coffee shop.
The store was a
"cosplay" coffee shop.
The assailant waited till
the shop had closed,
and is thought to have
entered from the rear door.
[GIRL]
Hey, sweetcheeks!
Hmm?
You free? Wanna have
some fun with us?
Say, you're pretty young.
Are you a high
school student...?
Huh?
Hey, wait!
Damn. This sucks.
And he was cute, too!
Okay, that's it for
the cleaning.
(Locks door)
The boss has her own key.
Better safe than
sorry, I guess...
I can't believe
I've got ANOTHER Mall
Committee meeting tonight!
They hold them all
in one month,
regular meetings as
well as idea exchanges
and financial
advisory meetings.
I even have to submit
my account ledgers!
It's such a huge pain
in the you‐know‐what!
Now the Mall Committee
Chair is like, "We need
a cutesy character"
and keeps shoving this weird
mascot character thing
into our faces.
I don't know what to do!
Maybe I should write
a song about it!
(Singing)
Mall committees are so stupid!
Anyway, I promise you'll never
ever have to watch the store
all by yourself again
if you'll just keep an eye
on it for one more night!
Pretty please?!
Once I'm done I'll race back
here at the speed of light
and I'll even bring you a snack!
I'm sorry!
I‐it's all right, ma'am.
Well, I don't really think I've
got anything to worry about...
Hm?
Ow! This could really
do some damage.
(Door unlocking)
Ma'am?
Ma'am? Huh?
I could've sworn I heard
the door being unlocked...
(Gasp)
Misa...
We let ourselves in.
I hope you don't mind
Don't move!
Let's go upstairs.
(Handcuffs locking)
(Creepy laughing)
We finally got you, Misa...
Just sit there
like a good girl, okay?
I don't wanna
have to get ugly.
That's right.
[MISAKI]
These guys... They're customers!
Hmm...
[FAT STALKER]
Misa...
We get it now.
[THIN STALKER]
Misa, to us...
You're the
perfect maid!
We've been watching you
this entire time,
even when you ignored us
and talked to other guys.
[THIN STALKER]
But we know the truth‐
you don't want anything
to do with them.
[THIN STALKER]
We're not like
those other guys.
We know who you
REALLY are, Misa.
(Misa roars)
(Terrified cry)
You morons!
You must be dreaming!
You know who I "really" am?
YEAH RIGHT!
If you wanna know the REAL me,
then step right up!
Wah!
Fierce glare!
Ahhh!
Aaah!
Serves you idiots right!
(Snickers)
Hahaha!
Huh?! Usui!
Ahh! The window's broken!
Oh, boy.
The boss is going to faint
when she sees this.
The back door was locked.
I had no choice.
[Stalkers sobbing]
[BOTH]
We're so sorry.
So tell me something.
What kind of person did you two
imagine that Misa really was?
I'm curious.
[THIN STALKER]
W‐well, we thought that
even though she's a maid,
she's really a sadist.
[FAT STALKER]
That's why we wanted her,
uh, we wanted her to
punish us severely.
Gah!
Oh. So you guys are
masochists, then?
Yeah, well...
Most definitely.
Hate to break it to you
but this cute little maid
belongs to me and me alone.
So hands off, got it?
Usui! You son of a...
I'm not your damn pet!
Get a move on.
Uh, it's just...
it'a just...!
You know...
It's only right to say
what should be said...
I mean... I...
Usui...
Umm... Thank you.
[SATSUKI]
Misa! I'm sorry
I'm back so late!
Oh, Usui!
You're here, too how nice!
Welcome back, ma'am...
but uhm‐
Were you two lovebirds
gazing into each other's
eyes right now?
Sorry for interrupting.
I should've taken
my time coming back.
Sorry, I'm not the most
observant woman.
Please don't say
things like that...
Huh? What is it, Usui?
You want me to look up...?
Oh, no!
What on Earth
happened here?
Sorry, ma'am.
The truth is...
(Fainting)
Manager!
So, did you cry for help?
"Eek, save me!"
Like a damsel in distress?
No, I taught them a lesson
they'll never forget.
I knew it.
The most important thing
is that you weren't hurt.
Don't ever be
so reckless again!
(Sigh)
Sorry guys.
I didn't mean
to make you worry.
But never fear‐ I'll make sure
to be even stronger next time!
Well, I guess that's
our Misaki for you.
She's already preparing
for her next battle.
(Awkward laugh)
The real question is why you'd
want to be stronger
than you are now.
O‐kay! Here.
I changed your
background picture.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Ah!
Wh‐when did you...?!
Wait a minute‐
who took this?!
Oh that would be me!
"If it's cute it has to be
loved by all,"
that's what our manager
always says, right?
She took enough pictures to
fill up her entire memory card.
Lemme see!
No way!
Let me see,
let me see!
Hey!
She's so cute!
Don't look, Usui!
Hey, that's no fair.
I want one.
Well...
Tah‐dah!
I happen to have
that photo saved, too.
Th‐this isn't funny‐!
Whoa. Gimme.
No, don't send him that!
Wait a second! How do I‐
How do I change this?
I can't have this
as my background!
I'll be too embarassed
to even use my phone!
What do I do?
But if I told you how to do it,
then it wouldn't be any fun,
now would it?!
And sent.
Cut it out, dammit!
Got it.
(Misaki crying)
[SUZUNA]
Misaki, those cakes
were delicious.
Tell your boss
I really enjoyed them.
I get the feeling Mom and I
will have plenty of cakes
coming our way soon.
[MISAKI]
Well you can't just
expect that‐
[USUI]
Miss President! I've got plenty
of Maid Latte points saved up.
[MISAKI]
You're there too often, Usui!
[USUI]
Let's take a picture
together, okay?
[MISAKI]
First, you'll have to
beat me at a game!
[USUI]
Oh, Miss President!
Next time you'll
get some disciples
who'll call you "Master."
[MISAKI]
What are you talking about?!