Welcome back, Master.
Misa's wearing glasses!
Niiice!
Oh!
[CUSTOMERS]
Huh?
My apologies, Masters.
M‐my apologies.
I'm sorry, Subaru.
Don't worry about it.
Kay...
Do your best, Misa!
We're cheering you on!
Oh, yeah!
This is bad...
I've gotta concentrate.
Misa, are you all right?
Oh! Manager,
sorry about that.
If something's bothering you,
I'm here to listen.
You can tell me
anything, okay?
Well, bye!
Sorry again!
It's all right. I know I can
always rely on you, Misa!
What about me?
Of course.
I rely on all of you!
Honoka, Subaru, Erika,
Gon, and Sayuri, too!
You're awfully trusting,
aren't you Manager?
Honoka, your aura
is oozing evil...
But I will get angry at
people who slack off
too much don't forget it!
Whoops! Guess that's my cue
to get back out there!
Misa, your shift's over, right?
See you tomorrow.
Thank you very much.
(Sigh)
That was no good...
Looks like fun.
Usui! You've already
been discharged?!
Yeah, I rock. Remember?
What are you thinking?
You're still wrapped up
in bandages!
Oh my, are you
worried about me?
NO! And quit
barging in here!
I couldn't help it‐
I just wanted to see my
Misa as soon as possible.
Ah! Stop it!
(Gasp)
I love you, Ayuzawa.
(Phone rings)
Sakura?
Huh? Misaki! Over here!
(Out of breath)
Who did they fight?
They fought a student
from Miyabigaoka.
It's that super elite
private school that only
rich kids go to!
This is bad‐ that's the kinda
place we don't want to
get in trouble with!
What a mess.
Excuse me.
Please, let me through.
Hey, you two!
What's going on over here?
What happened!
Ah! What the heck
is she doing here?!
How should I know?!
And who are you?
I'm Misaki Ayuzawa,
student council president of
Seika High School.
Is there some
kind of problem?
One of your so‐called "students"
suddenly lashed out at me
for no reason.
Is this true?!
(Groans)
I had heard that Seika students
were nothing but barbarians.
Now I can see that the rumors
are completely true.
I suggest that you consider
how you are going to
apologize for your behavior.
Don't screw with us!
What the hell should we
apologize to YOU for?!
You idiots...!
Be quiet!
Owww!
What was that for?!
If you hit him,
you have to apologize!
Huh?!
[ISHIDA]
No way! He deserved it!
[TAKAMIZAWA]
And YOU'RE the one
who's hitting people!
[MISAKI]
Shut up! Think of all
the people out here
who you're inconveniencing!
Only idiots resort to violence!
It appears that they are
incapable of conversing civilly.
I shall await you at
Miyabigaoka at your
earliest convenience.
If you do not apologize
for your actions...
we will be forced to report this
incident to our student council.
Hey, blow it out your ass!
Let's go.
Hey, wait a second!
Misaki!
What are we
going to do now?
For something
like this to happen
just as Seika was finally
improving its image...
If they don't apologize,
your hard work will go
straight out the window!
Don't worry about it...
I'll think of something.
That's what I said, but...
there's no way those guys
are just gonna agree
to go apologize.
I heard about Miyabigaoka.
(Misaki falling down)
What's going on?
Miss President,
are you all right?
It's nothing.
What's the matter, Ayuzawa?
This isn't the time to be
thinking about that!
I have to focus...
It's heavy... so heavy!
Excuse me! Could someone
please give me a hand?
Mr. Usui!
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
As for my reward...
That'll do just fine.
Yukimura!
Snap out of it!
Yukimura! Yukimuraaaa!
(Hysterical giggle)
I get it now. He's just a...
a sexually harassing idiot!
Now it makes total sense!
He just harasses whoever
happens to be closest!
(Misaki rants)
Does anyone else have any
idea what's going on...?
No idea‐ in fact, I don't
even think I WANT to know.
[MISAKI]
He really had me going there,
didn't he?! HAHAHA!
Seriously, what the hell
is your problem?
It looked like fun,
so I decided to tag along.
Besides, I haven't been
on a bus in awhile...
Why the heck is Usui coming?
And why do we even hafta go to
apologize in the first place?
If you don't wanna apologize,
then tell me why you were
fighting in the first place!
(Groan)
Fine, we'll tell you.
That day, we...
Chess, huh?
If we could play that,
it'd be so cool...
Whoa, that's expensive!
Dude, you can barely
even play checkers.
[KOGANEI]
My, how unusual.
Are those Seika High students?
This store belongs
to my family.
It's not the place for lowlifes
such as yourselves.
Begone, you insects.
(Grunt)
After that jerk said
somethin' like that...
Why would we apologize to him?!
What? We told you and
we still have to do it anyway?!
Man, I knew tellin' her
was pointless...
Is this place really
Miyabigaoka High School?
It's like a mansion...
[KOGANEI]
So you finally make
your grand appearance,
students of Seika High.
Oh, my. And it would appear
that you've made an
addition to your party.
Would this be the Student
Council Vice President?
No. I'm just taking
a field trip.
Huh? Is that so?
(Laughter)
What is it?
Really...?!
Well then, gentlemen‐
whenever you're ready.
I look forward to seeing
how you will apologize
for your misconduct.
Hurry up now
I have't got all day.
Tch!
Ha!
What's the matter?
Refusing to take responsibility
for your actions?
Why am I not surprised?
This is why
I despise commoners...
Very well. Looks like
I have no choice
to but take this discussion
to the student council.
"Foolish commoners," huh?
Now I get it.
Guess your crappy
attitude explains
why you think it's okay to
call our students "insects."
If you want to take
this "discussion"
to the student council,
then go right ahead.
In fact, take it
wherever you want!
I don't care if the entire
school finds out about it.
However‐
before you do any of that,
I want an apology
from YOU first.
Uh! And why
should I have to?
Because you have to
take responsibility
for your actions‐
if you'd just kept
your mouth shut they
never would've hit you.
To tell you the truth,
I'd like to get in
a few hits, too.
Yeah, count me in.
If you rally think
you can get away with
calling our students
"insects," you're dead wrong!
I demand an apology!
What nonsense is this?
Where's the harm in calling
an insect an insect?
Well. Then shall we settle
this with a chess match?
Huh?!
If you can defeat me,
I shall concede that the
students of Seika High
are not "insects",
and formally apologize.
Yeah right!
We don't even
know how to play!
This guy's really
startin' to piss me off!
Miss President?
I can only do shogi.
Then I guess
I'll give it a shot...
Huh?!
I suppose I could explain the
rules for you, if you want‐
No thanks. I played a bit
when I was younger,
so I think I'll be fine.
Is that so?
Oh, you can go first
if you want.
I can't figure him out...
Oh, I forgot to
mention to you:
this year I ranked fourth
place in the national
chess tournament.
So what?
"So" I guess I'll have to
go a little easy on you.
How thoughtful of you.
But don't worry...
Feel free to come at me
with everything you've got.
And if I win, I want you to
tell our student president
that she's a
beautiful butterfly.
Wh‐what are you saying?!
What about us?
But if I go all out there's no
way you could possibly beat me‐!
Uh!
Hey, doesn't that guy
look a little flustered?
Could it be that
Usui's actually winning?
I don't believe it!
Hmm...
What'll it be?
Do you give up?
Hmph! N‐not a chance!
(Chuckle)
What will you do now?
And checkmate.
AH!
That was so easy!
Another round?
(Laughing)
Hey, keep your voices down!
You're being rude to
the other passengers!
Did you see the
look on his face?!
"A game like this says nothing
about one's character."
Can you believe that guy?!
Insects! The students
of Seika High are
nothing but insects!
I refuse to breathe
the same air
as you heathens!
I bet he went home and
cried to his mommy!
Loser!
(Laughing)
That was awesome!
Usui, Miss President‐
thank you!
You two shouldn't so cocky,
after all, you were
at fault, too.
The next time something
like this happens‐
Then next time...
we'll ask for your advice!
Oh...
Geez, those guys
are such a handful...
You're quite the handful
yourself, Miss President.
Do you think that the other
Miyabigaoka students
think like that guy?
I'm sure they're not
ALL that bad.
In fact, I bet being rich comes
with its own set of problems
we can't even imagine...
Thus, Mr. President, I request
that we demand a formal apology
from Seika High at once!
Its students are as
undisciplined as
they are dangerous.
The very fact that, out of
that school full of men,
they chose a WOMAN
as their president,
clearly shows their‐
Shut up, Koganei.
Huh...
Those guys're from Miyabigaoka.
What the hell are
THOSE GUYS doing at Seika?
Miss President!
What is it?
Miyabigaoka's student
council president!
Huh?
That guy's the heir to the
Igarashi Conglomerate!
I've seen him
in magazines!
What should we do?
Do you think he's come
to complain to Misaki?
Don't worry. I'm sure Misaki
will be able to handle
things just fine.
I am Tora Igarashi,
Miyabigaoka's Student
Council President.
And what business does
Miyabigaoka's president
have with us today?
It would appear that a student
from our school has greatly
offended you.
My humblest apologies.
Uh...
Oh!
I have taken the liberty of
contacting the school president
to request that he be
expelled immediately.
E‐expelled?
That's way too excessive!
Our students were
the ones who hit him!
Then may I humbly ask for
your forgiveness, ma'am?
My forgiveness?
You didn't have to come
all the way over here
to ask something like that...
Well then, may I request
that he not be expelled?
Yes, of course.
I'm relieved to hear
you say that.
And I'm pleased to see
the rumors about you
have proven to be true.
Rumors?
Yes. I'd heard that you always
think of your students first,
and that you are not only fair,
but considerate as well.
Oh, wow! He's so polite!
And such good manners‐ he's
quite the gentleman isn't he?
(Boys laughing)
You better run!
You're never
gonna catch me!
Those guys are
screwing around again!
Stop right there!
Ah!
(Misaki roars)
Oh!
Stay with me!
I told you, quit running
around like morons
and use that energy to STUDY!
Oh crap! I completely forgot
about President Igarashi!
[IGARASHI]
Wonderful!
To think‐ you are as strong
as you are beautiful!
You are truly an amazing
woman, Miss President!
To be honest, I did not simply
come here to apologize,
but to ask you for
a favor as well.
Misaki Ayuzawa, would you
please do me the honor
of joining the Miyabigaoka
Student Council?
Huh?
Huuuh...?
Wait a second...
that doesn't make
any sense at all.
I can't be on the student
council of a school that
I don't even go to...
You would transfer,
of course.
We will make the arrangements
for your uniform,
as well as anything else
you might require.
Y‐yeah, but‐! I'm from
a really poor family,
and there's no way we
could afford the tuition
at a fancy place like that!
It's just not possible‐
Then how about this:
I'll prepare a scholarship
exclusively for you.
For someone as talented
and hardworking as yourself,
I'm sure all expenses
would be covered.
I can't ask you to‐
I will personally ensure
that you have everything
you could ever need.
Please consider my offer...
Miss Ayuzawa.
[IGARASHI]
Well then, I suppose we
should be on our way.
I'll be eagerly
awaiting your response.
President Igarashi,
I don't think I can...
Miss Misaki Ayuzawa...
Before you graced these
hallways with your presence,
Seika High was a
completely different
school than it is today.
But under your guidance,
the current student council has
come together to make a campus
that is truly impressive.
It is truly a school
to be proud of.
Damn, it was hot in there!
No surprise, I guess.
That broke‐ass school
can't even afford a REAL AC.
Still... HAHA!
Did you see when she
clotheslined that one guy?!
That was friggin' hilarious!
She threw'im
right on the ground!
She's way more interesting
than I thought...
I like her... Misaki Ayuzawa.
I'm lookin' forward to seeing
how things play out. Maki.
Sir.
Keep an eye on that chick
and don't let her outta
your sight, got it?
Sir.
[SHIROKAWA]
Aw, c'mon.
It's girls only today?!
Man, this blows.
[SARASHINA]
We can't even see
through the glass!
Welcome back to Maid Latte.
Swoooooon.
Would you like me to
show you to your seats?
O‐okay!
Oh!
Please watch your step, My Lady.
You're so cool, Mr. Misa!
That's Misa for you!
She's a natural!
It's thanks to her that
we could even pull an event
like this off
in the first place.
She's almost more popular
with the girls than she
is with the boys‐
they're practically melting!
I can't believe it!
This is the first time the shop
has been completely boy‐free!
I'm so happy!
This is going to be fun!
You seem awfully
pleased, Mr. Misaki.
Because I'm so popular.
Yeah, with other girls.
Shut it, you!
I'm a man at heart, anyway!
But still...
Huh?
It sure feels nice to get
so many compliments.
Woo‐hoo! Woo‐hoo!
If guys acted more like this,
I might cut them a little
slack every now and then.
What do you mean?
Like if they were
kinder to women,
and trustworthy,
and more gentlemanly.
So, you mean...
like me?
NO!
Then like Miyabigaoka's
student council president?
W‐what are you talking about?
This doesn't have
anything to do with him!
Quit running your mouth and
just get back to work already!
Do you know what
you'd like to order?
No, I'm having trouble
making up my mind.
Well then, why don't I
help you decide, Miss?
Mr. Misaki,
you're the coolest!
I wish there were more
boys out there like you!
Thank you.
So, which one would Mr. Misaki
be in a relationship?
Duh, it's totally obvious!
That deep voice,
those sultry eyes!
She's the dominant one!
Well, I wouldn't mind seeing
her on the receiving end!
Ooh, I'd totally
like to see that!
What the heck are they
talking about?
I know right!
[GIRL]
This is so awesome. I wish
I could come here every day.
In that case,
I'd recommend this one.
You'd like to know
MY favorite dish?
Here.
You'd like to feed me?
Say "Aaah."
Aaah.
[GIRLS]
She's perfect...
a little too perfect!
Girls sure are cute!
They're way more pure and
charming than men are.
Maybe I'll start dressing
as a boy from now...
But what were those
two girls talking about?
Being dominant?
And receiving?
Hey, Usui, do you
know what those mean?
You really want
me to tell you?
Wh‐what the heck
are you doing?!
I was all sweaty,
so I wanted to
change my undershirt.
Aren't you going
to change, too?
I'm not going to change
while you're here!
Why not? Weren't you
the one who said you
were a man at heart?
B‐but the others could‐
What's wrong?
Hurry up and strip.
Or would you prefer
I strip you instead...
Mr. Misaki?
Stop it...
Well, well.
Looks like you ARE a girl
after all, Ayuzawa.
Now you know what it means
to be the "dominant" one.
I've had enough of this.
How long do you think
you can keep messing
with me like this?
I don't want to see you
ever again, Usui.
Just leave me alone.
Sir, here's the report
you requested on
Misaki Ayuzawa.
Oh!
Haha! No freakin' way!
I don't believe it...
that girl really is
somethin' else, isn't she?
Thanks to this, I've
just thought up a very
special welcome party
for Miss Misaki Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI]
I never thought I'd be
offered the chance to
attend a school
like Miyabigaoka...
But if I transferred,
Seika would just go back
to the way it was before,
and the girls would be
totally defenseless.
[USUI]
You worry too much,
Miss President.
Instead of thinking
about yourself,
you're too concerned with
leaving the girls behind.
And if you went to Miyabigaoka,
you may not able to work at
the Maid Latte anymore...
[MISAKI]
Usui! Didn't I say I never
wanted to see you again!
[USUI]
Oh, that's right.
See you, Miss President.