[music playing]
[SAKURA] Huh?
[SAKURA] I must've just imagined
it..
[FANGIRL B] Yuuji!
[FANGIRL C] So cool!
[FANGIRL D] Lucky!
[MISAKI] Next Wednesday?
[SAKURA] Yeah! You're free after
class, right?
We're gonna throw a great big
partyyy!
[SHIZUKO] It's just a get
together with some band members.
[MISAKI] A band?
[SHIZUKO] Yes. They just so
happen to be
students of Yumesaki High
School...
[SAKURA] They're an indie‐label
band,
but they're super duper popular!
[SAKURA] They invited me
to hang out and told me
to bring all my friends!
Apparently, Sakura is
madly in love
with the band's lead singer.
She won't stop
talking about him.
[SAKURA] Shizuko, stop,
you're embarrassing me!
[MISAKI] L‐love?
Yeah, I'm totally crazy
about him!
That's why I really
want you to come
so I can introduce you to him.
[SAKURA] You'll come, won't you
Misaki?
[MISAKI] Uh, yeah but, are you
really sure
you want me to come, too?
[SAKURA] Of course I'm sure!
[USUI] Huh? President, you're
not going home yet?
[USUI] The student council
meeting's already over, isn't
it?
[MISAKI] Yeah, it ended awhile
ago.
I wanna get a head start on some
of my work before I leave.
I have a day I wanna free up
next week.
[MISAKI] This one goes here...
[USUI] You have plans or
something?
[MISAKI] Sakura said she wants
to get together after class.
[USUI] Just the two of you?
[MISAKI] No‐ Shizuko, too.
Where exactly does this go...?
[USUI] What are you going to do?
[MISAKI] We're gonna meet up
with some guy band.
I don't remember the name of it‐
[MISAKI] Ah, this goes HERE!
So then this one...?
[USUI] A "guy band"? You mean a
"boyband"?
[MISAKI] Yeah. Huh? Where the
heck does this go?
[USUI] But you don't know them?
[MISAKI] Would you just leave me
alone already!
I can't focus on my filing!
Get outta here and go home!
[USUI] What, that? Doesn't it go
right here?
[USUI] And, what will you all be
doing?
[MISAKI] I don't know! Talking
at a coffee shop or something, I
guess.
[USUI] Is that so...
[MISAKI] What is it? You want to
say something, don't you?
[USUI] No. It's just unusual for
you to do something like that.
[MISAKI] That's true. The last
time I got to hang out after
class
was probably back
when I was in middle school.
[MISAKI] I guess that's why I'm
really looking forward to it!
[SAKURA] Here! Look!
[MISAKI] So this is the band?
Make sure to listen to the whole
CD before the party, okay?
[SAKURA] Their songs just give
you that warm, happy feeling!
[MISAKI] Have you listened to
their music, Shizuko?
[SHIZUKO] Yes, unfortunately.
[MISAKI] Did it give you a warm,
happy feeling?
[SHIZUKO] Actually, it had quite
the opposite effect.
[MISAKI] A warm happy feeling,
huh?
[SUZUNA] Recently, there've been
less.
[MISAKI] Less what?
[SUZUNA] Of these postcards.
Now most of them want you
to apply online.
[MISAKI] What's the big prize
for this magazine's giveaway?
[SUZUNA] A year's supply of
crab.
[MISAKI] Huh? But isn't this
a music magazine?
Well, now that you point it out,
it does seem kinda strange.
[MISAKI] I guess they're pretty
popular...
[SATSUKI] Is that Yumemishi I
hear?
[MISAKI] Ma'am, you know them?
[SATSUKI] Of course I do!
Even though they're an
indie‐label band
they're really popular!
Still, I only got
into them recently.
[SATSUKI] Hey, what do you think
about having
a "Rocker Chick Day" at the
shop?
[MISAKI] A Rocker Chick Day,
huh?
[MISAKI] I'll have that out
right away. If you'll excuse me.
[MISAKI] Come to think of it...
[MISAKI] I haven't seen THEM
recently. [TRIO] Misa, Misa,
Misa!
[MISAKI] Hopefully they're
spending more time
focusing on their schoolwork.
[SHIZUKO] I was surprised.
[MISAKI] By what?
That you agreed to attend
Sakura's so‐called "party."
[SHIZUKO] That type of music
doesn't strike me
as something you would normally
enjoy.
[MISAKI] What can I say?
Sakura seemed so excited
that I didn't have any choice
but to say "yes."
[SHIZUKO] I just hope everything
goes well...
[MISAKI] Huh?
[SHIZUKO] Ah, never mind it's
nothing.
[SAKURA] Sorry I'm late!
[SAKURA] It's finally tomorrow,
huh?
[KUROSAKI] Oooho! We've saved up
quite a bit.
[SARASHINA] Just a little
more and my dream will
finally become reality!
[SHIROKAWA] You mean OUR dream.
[TRIO] THE dream!
[TRIO] A Single‐Day Splurge
of All Maid Latte Menu Items!
[TRIO] And don't forget!
[SARASHINA] We'll have enough
points
to challenge Misa to another
card game!
[SHIROKAWA] This time we will
not lose!
[KUROSAKI] We'll get our photo
with Misa no matter what!
[SARASHINA] All right, let's put
in another solid day's work!
[KUROSAKI] Shiroyan, don't break
any dishes today!
[SHIROKAWA] And you, don't get
any orders wrong.
[SARASHINA] Oh, we already have
some customers.
[KUROSAKI] Welcome them!
[SHIROKAWA] Hello, welcome to‐
Huh?
Shock!
[SAKURA] Shizuko, how do my
bangs look?
[SHIZUKO] This is the sixth time
you've asked today‐
they look the same.
Waagh! But today
is a special day!
They have to look perfect!
[SAKURA] Hey, Misaki, Shizuko's
being mean to me again!
[MISAKI] Don't worry,
I think they look really good.
[SAKURA] Huh?
[MISAKI] Your bangs.
Really?! Misaki, thank you!
[MISAKI] I'm glad I came.
[SHIROKAWA] What a shocker...
[KUROSAKI] It's like the tables
have been turned...
[SARASHINA] I wonder what
they're doing here...
Heh. I'll take their order.
Nah, you can just go ahead and
leave this to me...
No no, I should be the one to
go...
[KUROSAKI] If anyone should go
it should be me!
[SHIROKAWA] No way! You make too
many mistakes!
[KUROSAKI] What'd you say to
me!?
[TRIO] Aaagh! They're so bright!
[SAKURA] Hey, Kuuga! Over here!
[KUUGA] Hey.
[MISAKI] This is...
[MISAKI] the guy Sakura likes?
[TRIO] HEY!
[SARASHINA] What is this? What
the hell is this?!
[SHIROKAWA] Are they on some
kinda group date or something?!
[KUUGA] Well, guess we should
introduce ourselves.
[SHOU] I'm Shou, the guitarist.
[KOU] I'm Kou, the bassist.
[KUUGA] Hii! I'm Kuuga, the lead
singer!
[YUUJI] I'm the drummer, William
Adam Yuuji. Howdy!
[MISAKI] So... You're not from
around here, are you?
[YUUJI] That's nice, Misa.
[KUUGA] Nice rebound on that
one!
[MISAKI] I've never met people
like this before.
I'm not really sure what to
say....
[KUUGA] Oh, Sakura!
I brought you a special gift‐
it's a limited edition poster.
[SAKURA] No way? Really?!
[SAKURA] AAAAH, they're so
coool!
[MISAKI] It's no good.
I can't keep up with Sakura's
level of excitement at all.
[MISAKI] What about Shizuko?
[SHIZUKO] People are like
garbage...
[MISAKI] She's completely
checked‐out!
[SAKURA] It's really, really not
a dream, right?
[YUUJI] What do you mean?
Right now, having all
the members of my favorite band
right here in front of me!
I still can't believe it...
I'm so happy I became a fan!
[YUUJI] You're exaggerating.
[SAKURA] No, I'm not at all!
[SAKURA] I love Yumemishi.
The very first time I heard
Kuuga's voice...
[SAKURA] I was so happy...
my heart was racing so fast
I thought it'd never stop.
So what if I'm not as excited
as she is to be here?
[MISAKI] Sakura really likes
this guy.
And if he makes her happy,
then I want to support her.
[KOU] Still, she only brought
two friends with her...
[KOU] Guess there wasn't a point
in bringing those 20 tickets.
[KUUGA] Let's just quit doing
these stupid fan events. They're
a waste of time.
[KUUGA] We've got enough people
coming to our shows.
[KOU] But that one girl seems
really crazy about you, huh?
[KUUGA] Who cares.
That girl with the long,
straight hair's way hotter.
[KUUGA] She said her name was
Misaki, right?
That girl‐ she's the one I wanna
get with.
[TRIO]
[SHIROKAWA] Misa?!
[KUROSAKI] "Get with her"?!
[SARASHINA] What the hell?!
What should we do?
Our Misa will be...!
[MISAKI] A live show?
[KUUGA] Yeah!
What do you say, Misa!
It'll be a lot of fun, I
promise!
[MISAKI] Uh, sorry, but I don't
have
a lot of free time in my
schedule...
[KUUGA] And what about you?
[SHIZUKO] I'll pass, thanks.
[SAKURA] C'mon you guys!
[SAKURA] After all these tickets
are really hard
to get a hold of, aren't they
Kuuga‐
[KUUGA] Aw, don't be
like that, Misaki,
I'm sure you can find a way to
come!
[MISAKI] Huh?
Well I don't have a lot of money
either...
[KUUGA] Then I'll just give you
that ticket for free.
[KUUGA] You gotta come... won't
you, Misaki?
[MISAKI] Uh, well, that is, I...
[MISAKI] S‐Sakura, are you
going?
[SAKURA] Huh? Yeah, you bet I
am!
[YUUJI] Sakura you come to every
single show of ours, dontcha?
[MISAKI] Really? Every show?
Wow, Sakura, you're one devoted
fan!
She's always telling us about
you guys and how great you are.
[MISAKI] You really like them,
don't you?
[KUUGA] So, Misaki...
[KUUGA] Are you sure you can't
come to our live show?
Not even... for me?
[MISAKI] Is it my imagination?
I feel like that Kuuga
guy is only talking to me.
[MISAKI] What should I do about
Sakura?
[KUUGA] Hey there!
Wh‐what are you doing here?!
[KUUGA] Well, I thought you and
I
could have a nice little chat...
[MISAKI] Then we can do that
back at the table with
everyone else.
[KUUGA] Nah, it's cool.
The others are covering for me
with your friends.
[MISAKI] What are you saying?
You know how Sakura
feels about you, don't you?
[KUUGA] Yeah, but it's not like
I'm actually interested in her.
[MISAKI] Then why did you invite
her in the first place?!
[KUUGA] It was just a little
event for the fans, of course.
[KOU] But that girl seems pretty
serious.
She's gonna end up getting hurt.
[KUUGA] So what? I can't
hang out with every single
one of my fans.
I have to decide who makes the
cut.
[MISAKI] But that's‐
[KUUGA] It's what?
[KUUGA] It's kindness, really.
I reject them right away
and let'em down nice and easy.
[KUUGA] They're just gonna end
up getting hurt either way,
so better sooner than later,
right?
[MISAKI] What're you saying...?
[KOU] Hey!
[KUUGA] Still...
[KUUGA] If YOU became a fan...
[KUUGA] I'd make an exception.
[USUI] My apologies for the
wait.
I'd be delighted tp take your
orders.
[MISAKI] U‐! Usui! What are you
doing here?!
[USUI] Oh, so sorry, sir.
[MISAKI] U‐! Usui!
What are you doing here?!
[KUUGA] Who the heck
is this guy?!
Do you know him, Misaki?!
[KOU] He's her boyfriend isn't
he?
At least, judging by
the timing he is.
[MISAKI] N‐no! Not at all!
You're way off!
[KUUGA] What, then?!
[USUI] Her stalker, of course.
[KUUGA] Is there another waiter
we can talk to?
[MISAKI] Uh, no no! It's fine,
really!
He's a not a stalker he's a...
[MISAKI] He's a stalker but NOT
a stalker.
Uh, that is, I mean... Geez I
don't know what I mean... But
really, it's‐
[KUUGA] Whatever.
This is too weird for me.
Enjoy yourselves.
[USUI] A stalker but not a
stalker, huh? Then what?
Anyway, what do you
think you're doing?
And since when did you start
working here?
[USUI] I don't work here.
[MISAKI] Then where'd you get
that uniform from...?
[SHIROKAWA] Just let it all out.
[USUI] Well, I just happened to
run into an associate of mine...
And I had the sudden urge
to take it off him.
[MISAKI] There's something
really wrong with you, isn't
there?
[USUI] It couldn't be helped.
There are some things that
just really irritate me.
[MISAKI] Well just because
they're irritating
doesn't mean you can do whatever
you want‐
[USUI] On top of that, I'm VERY
possessive.
Especially around guys like
that.
[MISAKI] That...!
That's got nothing
to do with you!
[MISAKI] Don't get the wrong
idea.
The only reason I'm here,
is because of Sakura...
[SAKURA] I'm totally crazy about
him!
[SAKURA] That's why I really
want you to come
so I can introduce you to him.
[MISAKI] Sakura was...
she was really looking forward
to this...
then this happened...
[USUI] What a face you're
making, Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI] I can't help it.
I feel like I'm at a total
loss...
[MISAKI] I have no idea what the
best thing to do is...
[USUI] The best thing, huh?
[USUI] Nobody knows that, do
they?
[MISAKI] Why does he always do
that! Damnit.....
[KUUGA] Boooored...
[SAKURA] Um, Kuuga!
You'll be singing a new song at
your next live show, right?
[KUUGA] Yeah. Sure.
[SAKURA] I'm really looking
forward to it!
[KUUGA] Great...
[SAKURA] So then, what kind of
song is it gonna be?
[KUUGA] Well...
Oh, I'm sorry! I guess
I shouldn't have asked that!
[KUUGA] You know...
[SAKURA] Y‐yeah what is it?!
[KUUGA] Can't you find a way to
make it work out?
[SAKURA] Huh?
[KUUGA] With Misaki.
You guys are friends,
aren't you?
[SAKURA] Yeah...
Then get her
to come to our concert.
[SAKURA] Misaki... Misaki's
schedule is really busy.
She's Student Council President
and...
[KUUGA] No way! Misaki's the
student council president?
How cool!
[KUUGA] Not only is she cute,
but she's got brains, too.
[KUUGA] She knows how to dress
and think. She's pretty amazing,
huh?
[KUUGA] Say...
Come on, Sakura,
won't you ask her for me?
As a favor.
[KUUGA] What do you say?
[KUUGA] Oh, Misaki! Welcome
back!
[SAKURA] Hey, Misaki...
[SAKURA] I'd really like it
if you came to their next
concert with me.
[MISAKI] Huh?
I'll even help you out... with
your... student council
work if you want...
[MISAKI] S‐Sakura?
[SAKURA] It looks like...
It looks like Kuuga really
wants you to come, Misaki.
[SAKURA] The whole time you were
gone,
all he did was talk about you.
[SAKURA] It looks like Kuuga...
really likes you...
[KUUGA] So Misaki, you're the
student council president, huh?
[KUUGA] Since you're such a hard
worker
you deserve a break
every now and then!
[KUUGA] If you can't go to the
concert,
how about we got to an amusement
park instead?
[KUUGA] You act
all‐straightlaced
but I bet you know
how to show a guy a good time.
[KUUGA] You're pretty smart,
too.
You probably play the
field quit a bit, don't you?
[KOU] Hey, Kuuga!
[KUUGA] Was that waiter from
earlier one of your boyfriends?
[KUUGA] You tryin' to show off
or something?
[SAKURA] Stop it...
[KUUGA] What's this?
Since you're not speaking up,
that means I'm right,
doesn't it?
[SAKURA] Please...
[KUUGA] Wow! Seika's
Student Council President
sure is a wild one.
[SAKURA] Stop it!
[SAKURA] Please don't...
Please don't talk about Misaki
like that, I'm begging you!
[KUUGA] What's this Sakura...
do you hate me now?
[KOU] That's enough, Kuuga!
I told you to be more
respectful to the fans!
[KUUGA] Yeah, yeah. I know, I
know.
[MISAKI] I've had enough.
[MISAKI] Is this the "kindness"
you were talking about?
[MISAKI] If you ask me, that's
the biggest load of crap I've
ever heard.
Get over yourself already.
Sakura was really looking
forward to this day, and you've
ruined it.
You trampled on her feelings
without any regard for her at
all...
[KUUGA] Uh oh! Do you hate me
now, too, Misaki?
I don't hate you.
I DESPISE YOU!
[MISAKI] I'll never hand Sakura
over... to a piece of trash like
you!
[MISAKI] I'm sorry...
It's too late for that!
How could you raise your voice
like that while inside of a
restaurant?!
[SHIZUKO] I don't care how angry
you are,
be more considerate of the
people around you!
[SHIZUKO] Misaki, your temper is
way too short!
[MISAKI] I... I'm sorry...
[SHIZUKO] And Sakura have you
forgotten
what I've told you so
many times before?!
[SHIZUKO] You're way too easily
deceived,
so you need to choose your
friends more wisely!
[SAKURA] Waaaaah... I thought he
was a good guy!
[SHIZUKO] Well he wasn't!
You need to learn to read men
better!
[MISAKI] I don't think I've ever
seen Shizuko get this intense
before...
[SHIZUKO] That's what you get
for putting me in that kind of
situation.
[SHIZUKO] My temper has its
limits, too, you know!
[SAKURA] Shizuko, you're not
nice at all!
[SHIZUKO] Because if I go easy
on you,
you'll never learn your lesson!
Shizuko... I think she's had
enough for one day.
[SAKURA] Misaki!
[MISAKI] Um, uh, don't cry,
everything'll be fine...!
[SAKURA] The next time I fall in
love
it'll be with someone who pats
my head just like this.
[MISAKI] Sakura... I hope you
find a good guy soon.
[MISAKI] Next time you fall in
love, it'll be with someone who
pats your head, huh?
[USUI] Finally. You're back.
[USUI] You're late, Miss
President.
[USUI] Did you hurt your head or
something?
[MISAKI] Huh? Oh, n‐no, it's
nothing!
[MISAKI] And what are you doing
hanging around over here?!
[USUI] Nothing to get worked up
about. Just being a stalker.
[MISAKI] Huh?!
[USUI] Since I'm a stalker,
maybe I should follow you to
your house.
[MISAKI] Go away!
[KOU] Now look what you've done,
Kuuga!
Can't you just act like an adult
for once?
[KUUGA] Lay off, Kou!
Quit talking like you're my dad
or something!
[SHOU] On a more important
note...
[SHOU] What's with those guys?
[TRIO] Hurry up and get the hell
out of here
before we kick you to the curb,
Masters!
[SAKURA] Shizuko! You'll go to
the next Yumemishi concert with
me, right?
[SHIZUKO] Huh?! Sakura,
you STILL haven't learned?!
[SHIZUKO] But if it's boring,
we're all going home together.
[SAKURA] So you WILL come with
me? Yay! Oh, Misaki!
[MISAKI] Huh, Sakura? Shizuko?
What are you doing?
[SHIZUKO] I thought we'd do the
next episode preview,
but it's difficult, isn't it?
[SAKURA] We were waiting for
you, Misaki!
[USUI] Glance.
[SAKURA] Misaki, would you like
to come to Yumemishi‐
[MISAKI] Ah, sorry, Sakura. I'll
catch up with you later.
[USUI] Glance, glance.
[SHIZUKO] Huh? Usui seems to be
glancing at something
interesting.
[USUI] Glance, glance, glance,
glance! [SAKURA] More like he
wants us to be interested in
HIM.
[MISAKI] I have a feeling this
is going to be a pain...