[SHIROKAWA]
Tomorrow is the start of our
class field trip to the woods!
Five days and four
nights in nature!
We'll be playing tennis and
swimming by day,
and enjoying fresh‐cooked meals
and hot springs by night!
And we can catch unicorn beetles
and sell them for enough cash
to eat the entire Maid Latte
menu for a WHOLE WEEK!
AND I heard from one of the
seniors that
there's gonna be a beautiful
SINGLE babe in a white dress
staying at a nearby guest house!
[TRIO]
Whoaaa!
[SHINTANI]
(chewing) Is this outdoor
field trip thing really that
much fun?
You betcha! All the seniors
keep going on and on about
how great it is‐
[SHINTANI]
(huh) Ah! Misaki!
He ain't listening.
Well, we better get back
to our classroom.
We are in a different
class, after all...
[MISAKI] Stop eating bread
crusts while you walk!
(SHINTANI laughing)
(BOYS grunting)
[BOYS]
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
[TRIO]
This isn't right at all!
What the heck is this crap?!
Why are we at a temple?!
The field trip is supposed to be
about
"freedom, paradise, and
living life to its fullest!"
That's what all of
the seniors told us!
What the heck is going on?!
More importantly, where's the
hottie with the white dress at?!
We're high up in the mountains
that there's no one else around
for miles!
What were those crappy
seniors talking about?!
[MISAKI]
They were obviously
lying to you.
It's Seika's legendary "Fool
the Second‐Years," apparently.
[SHIROKAWA] "Fool
the Second‐Years"?
[MISAKI] I don't
know when it started,
but previous generations of
students who were disappointed
with this so‐called "field
trip," began telling lies
to the juniors
to make them look forward to it
so they could make themselves
feel better.
[BOYS] (shocked) Ahhh!
[SENIOR]
Huh? You wanna know about the
class field trip? Yeah, it was
SO much fun!
[BOY]
Um, sir, are you feeling okay?
[SENIOR]
It was so much fun
that I lost 20 pounds!
You guys are gonna
have the time of your life!
The food is great, and the
excursions are even better!
(chuckles)
[MISAKI]
Then the ones who got lied to
started lying to others,
resulting in a domino effect
that's gone on for generations.
[SARASHINA]
No way! That's so cruel!
[KUROSAKI] Our dreams
have been crushed!
[SHIROKAWA] This sucks!
[TRIO]
How are we supposed to
enjoy our field trip now?!
[MISAKI]
Quit whining! Make no mistake‐
this still counts as school. You
aren't here to goof off!
[MISAKI] Got it? Then hurry
up and get back to work!
[SHINTANI] Misaki!
[ALL] Huh?
[BOY A]
You're lookin' extra
air‐headed today, Hinata.
[BOY B]
Come to confess your love again?
[SHINTANI]
Let's have fuuuun‐!
[MISAKI]
This isn't free time. Go back to
your area, immediately.
[BOY C]
Aw, c'mon Pres,
don't be so hard on him!
[MISAKI]
It seems like you've forgotten
who you're talking to‐
guess I'll have to
jog your memory!
(BOYS panicking)
[YUKIMURA]
Mr. Usui, please stop that!
Ahhh! Miss President!
Please help me!
[MISAKI]
What do you think you're doing?
[USUI]
Nothing‐ just some
friendly cleaning.
[YUKIMURA]
That's a lie! I don't
know what's going on,
but he's been dragging
me all over the place!
[MISAKI]
I can see that. Don't
worry, Yukimura, I'll
deal with this pervert.
(YUKIMURA screaming)
[MISAKI]
I swear, what's with you?
I thought it was weird that I
hadn't seen you all day.
[MISAKI] What have
you been doing?
[BOY E] Hey, let's get out of
here.
[BOY F]
Hinata, come on!
[USUI]
Maybe I was just trying to make
a certain someone jealous.
[MISAKI] Ulp!
[USUI]
Was that bad?
[MISAKI]
Of course it's bad!
That's no excuse to goof off
and make fun of Yukimura!
[USUI]
Huh? I thought it
was a great reason.
Look, just hurry up
and finish cleaning!
[SHINTANI] Huh?
[MISAKI]
(sigh) What am I going to do...
Why are things always like that
between me and Usui?
[SHIZUKO] Oh. It's Misaki.
[MISAKI] Geh!
[SAKURA] You're already
getting ready, huh?
[MISAKI] Yeah. That's right.
[SAKURA]
Geez, between meditation and
lectures and cleaning, I'm all
worn out!
[SHIZUKO]
But the girls are fortunate
to be on dinner‐duty.
[SAKURA] That's for sure, the
boys have to sit under a
waterfall...
[BOYS] (dread) Uh....
[MISAKI]
You girls, if you're free, help
out with making the rice.
[MISAKI]
Also, the vegetable scraps are
being collected over there.
[GIRLS] Okay!
[GIRL] Do you need
anymore carrots?
[SAKURA]
Misaki, you sure are amazing.
You know how to get everyone
working so efficiently.
You think so? Thanks a lot.
I never would've thought to have
washed the pots and pans ahead
of time.
It's way easier this way.
[SHIZUKO]
None of us would have noticed
how dirty they were
until it was too late.
[MISAKI]
Well, that's because‐
[MISAKI, thinking]
It's because our manager at
Maid Latte is always so picky
about it...
[MISAKI, thinking]
But I can't say that.
[SAKURA] Because what?
[MISAKI] Uh, you know‐
[SAKURA]
BY THE WAY, HOW ARE THINGS WITH
YOU AND HINATA?!
Huh? Wh‐Where did that come
from? We weren't talking about
that at all!
[SAKURA]
That's cuz I've been dying to
know! It's killing me!!
[SHIZUKO]
Sakura's sole objective for this
field trip is to corner you
and pry every single detail of
your love life out of you.
You can't have a proper
field trip without talking
about love, right?!
Hinata showing up was
such nice timing, too!
[SHIZUKO] It would appear that
the others are extremely
interested as well.
[GIRLS] Huh? Huh? Huh?!
[MISAKI]
What's with all of you?!
Ugh. Guys...It's
not like that...
He's just a childhood
friend... that's all.
[SAKURA] Really? Are you sure
there's nothing going on between
you two?
[GIRLS] Huuuh?
[MISAKI]
No! Besides, I don't have
time for things like that!
[MISAKI]
(sigh) As Seika's Student
Council President I've got more
important things to worry about.
I can't look after him like
I did when we were kids.
(BOYS shivering)
[SHIROKAWA]
Gah, it's so cold!
[SARASHINA] It hurts!
[KUROSAKI] We're in Hell!
[SHINTANI]
This is awesome! Woohoo!
[BOY B]
Wait, don't tell me he's
actually enjoying this?
[BOY C]
It's like you were
raised in the wild.
[BOY D]
You're like an
elementary‐school kid.
[SHINTANI]
(chomp) Oh, you think so?
[BOY E]
Dude, what are you eating?
[BOY C]
You're just too stupid
to be afraid of things,
aren't you?
(bush rustling)
[SHINTANI] Huh?
[BOY D]
What is it, Hinata?
[BOY E]
Hey, don't mess with Usui!
(BOYS murmuring) (shocked gasps)
[SHINTANI]
You're the coolest guy I've ever
seen!
[SHINTANI] Whoa and you're
super muscular, too!
[SHINTANI] Wow! You're
body's perfect!
[BOY C] Hey, Hinata...
[BOY E] That's too dangerous.
If I were a girl, I'd fall
head over heels for you.
[YUKIMURA]
Ahhhh! N‐N‐N‐No! You can't
say something like THAT!
Don't you realize that's Mr.
Usui you're talking to?!
[SHINTANI]
Hm? Did I say somethin' wrong?
[YUKIMURA]
W‐wrong? If you're not careful,
you're going to get ravaged!
[SHINTANI]
What're you talkin' about?
I'm a man!
[YUKIMURA]
That doesn't matter to Mr. Usui‐
trust me I know!
[SHINTANI]
Whoa, what's that
delicious‐looking red fruit?
[YUKIMURA]
Huh? Wait a second, Shintani!
I'm not done talking here!
[PRIEST] Not only meditation and
cleaning, but eating, bathing
and even going to the restroom
will comprise your training.
On principle, all general
conversation is prohibited,
however tonight you may engage
in small talk. Now enjoy.
[STUDENTS]
Thank you for the meal.
[SHIROKAWA] Where's the rest?
[SARASHINA] All we get is
this tiny bowl of curry?
[KUROSAKI]
I thought this was meat,
but it's some kinda
meat‐shaped jelly!
[SHIROKAWA]
Is this what hell looks like?
[SHINTANI] Seconds, please!
[TRIO] Huh?
[SHINTANI] (happy) Wahhh!
[BOY B] Yo, Hinata...
[PRIEST]
There are no seconds, young man.
[SHINTANI]
Huh?! But this ain't enough!
[PRIEST]
Food should be chewed more
slowly and contemplated...
[SHINTANI]
I chewed it but it wasn't
enough!
There's no way someone could
just have one bowl‐ I'm so
hungry I'm gonna die!
[MISAKI, thinking]
What is that idiot doing?
[BOY F] He has to clean
outside as punishment?
At this time of night?
(SHINTANI groaning)
[BOY E]
I couldn't do it, even on a
dare. It's too scary!
[BOY C]
But knowing that Hinata, he'll
be out looking for more food
instead of cleaning.
[BOY D]
He'll probably end up eating
the snacks people left as grave
offerings or something, huh?
[BOY F] I could definitely see
that! Who knows what kinda
trouble he'll get into when he's
left on his own?
[MISAKI]
Got that right...
Oh, I swear!
[MISAKI]
Seriously, would it be too much
to ask that Shintani just stay
out of trouble for once?!
[MISAKI]
Where did that idiot go?
[SHINTANI]
Hrm, no flashlights in here
either...
[SHINTANI]
If I had some light, I could go
looking for food on the
mountain.
[MISAKI]
What do you think you're
doing, busting into the
storehouse like this!?
You trying to be a thief?
[SHINTANI]
Uh? Misaki? Nah... you've got
it all wrong.
I was just lookin' for a
flashlight‐ Ugh!
[MISAKI]
Shut up! We've gotta get out of
here right away!
If the men from the
temple find us here...
[PRIEST]
That's strange. What's this
doing open?
Hey, is somebody in there?
[PRIEST]
I guess someone forgot to close
it. How irresponsible...
[MISAKI]
He locked us in!
(struggling) It won't open!
[SHINTANI]
Doesn't look like there's any
other way out of here either.
[MISAKI]
(deflated) Why did I hide like
that?
[MISAKI]
If I'd just come forward and
explained the situation, he
might have listened to me...
[SHINTANI]
But... right now...
The two of us are trapped in
a locked room all alone at
night... be still my heart!
[SHINTANI]
D‐don't worry! I know what to
do‐ I read a story like this in
a manga once!
[SHINTANI]
Uh, first we have to secure the
food. Then we gotta find a way
to stay warm!
[MISAKI] Uh, it's not even cold
outside...
[SHINTANI] We don't have cell
phones, so wireless!
[SHINTANI] Yeah that's it‐
we gotta use the wireless!
[MISAKI] "Wireless"?
Ahhh! What should I do?! I‐I
can't lie in your naked embrace
till morning comes!
There's gotta be
some other way!
[MISAKI]
Just what kind of manga
have you been reading?
Misaki, aren't you nervous at
all?! It's just the two of us!
[MISAKI]
What the heck would I be nervous
about? We just have to hurry and
find a way out.
[SHINTANI] I...
[MISAKI] Huh?
[SHINTANI]
But the two of us... are
16‐years‐old, a man and woman.
[MISAKI]
Shin... tani...
Hey, Misaki I know that... you
may not've ever really thought
of me that way before but...
but from now on I'd like for ya
to look at me as a man. I'm not
that little boy any more.
[MISAKI] Uh?
[SHINTANI] Gah! (muttering)
[MISAKI] What is it?
What's wrong?
Nothing, it's just... this
kinda thing... is really
embarrassing.
[SHINTANI]
Oh no, what do I do?! My face is
all hot! I'm getting all red
aren't I?!
Huh? D‐don't look at me like
that! It's making it worse.
[MISAKI]
(giggle) First you tell me to
look at you, then not to look.
Do you want me to look at you or
not, Shintani? Just tell me.
[SHINTANI]
"Do I"? Well, I‐I want you to‐!
[USUI]
You want to be looked
at as a man, right?
[SHINTANI] Huh?!
[MISAKI] Usui!
[MISAKI] Uh? AH!
[USUI]
Well... If you want to be a
man... I'll show you.
(gasps)
[COACH]
You have already
completed three days here.
[COACH]
Tomorrow, your final day, you
will leave the temple and camp
outdoors.
[COACH B] And we will be taking
attendance.
(BOYS disheartened)
Looks like three days of hard
training have left the boys
so drained that they don't have
the energy to screw around.
[SAKURA]
But Misaki, I heard something
scary from one of the senior
girls...
[SHIZUKO] Rumor has it that on
the fourth day, the girls will
be put in grave danger.
[MISAKI] What?
[SHINTANI]
(battle cry) Prepare yourself,
Takumi Usui! HYAH!
[MISAKI]
(sigh) What the hell is up with
you two? You've been fighting
nonstop since last night!
[MISAKI]
Quit fighting like a
bunch of mangy dogs!
[SHINTANI] We're not fighting!
[MISAKI] (angry)
[SHINTANI]
This is a heated conversation
between MEN!
[SHINTANI] Ain't
that right, Takumi?
[USUI] That's right, Sanshita.
[SHINTANI] I'm tellin' ya,
my name's Hinata Shintani!
[USUI]
Huh? Isn't that what I said?
Shintani, Sanshita, same thing.
[SHINTANI]
It AIN'T the same thing!
[USUI] Fine how about, Mr. Pain
in the Ass? How about that?
[SHINTANI] That
ain't right, either!
[MISAKI] Sit down, shut up, and
think about what you've done!
[MISAKI]
I swear, those guys
are such a pain.
Couldn't they put that
unnecessary energy to a
better use?
[BOY B] There is no such thing
as "unnecessary" energy.
[MISAKI] Hmmm?
[BOY C]
Indeed. It is an excellent thing
to live with all one's strength.
[KUROSAKI]
A sound body and a sound mind
allow one to savor the true
flavor of happiness.
Though this fact tends to
be forgotten, lost to us.
[SARASHINA]
That we only realize this
through extremes points to
our own shortcomings as men
who have lost our path.
[SHIROKAWA]
In any case, we should
be off to bed.
[SHIROKAWA]
And give thanks for all the
blessings we have received on
this truly hallowed day.
[MISAKI, thinking]
All the boys... and even the
Three Idiots have achieved total
enlightenment!
[SHINTANI]
At this rate, I'm gonna get
eaten up by mosquitoes and
be so swollen tomorrow morning
that I'll look like a totally
different person!
[USUI]
That's really too bad.
[SHINTANI]
How come they're
not bothering you?
They're all over
the place out here!
[USUI]
You should be happy you're
so popular, Sanshita.
[USUI] Even though
they're just mosquitoes.
[SHINTANI] Look, quit
calling me "Sanshita"!
[USUI]
Better keep it down, or the
President'll shout at you again.
[SHINTANI]
Say... Takumi, do you like
Misaki? Or are you...
Are you two... Are you two
goin' out? You'd tell me
that wouldn't ya, Usui?
If we were going out, I wouldn't
be out here with you, would I?
[MISAKI]
Why did it have to rain so hard
TODAY of all days?
[SAKURA]
This was the one day we could
finally escape from the temple
and go camping! Oh....
[SHIZUKO]
It seems like the boys have
already completely turned into
zombies.
[SHIZUKO]
In that case, we may not have to
worry about what the senior
students told us after all.
[MISAKI]
What did they say again? The
girls would be put in "grave
danger" or something like that?
[GIRL A]
Look‐ we're finally here!
[GIRL A] There's a tennis court!
[GIRL B] I wanna get in right
now!
[GIRL C]
And a hot springs bath!
[MISAKI]
We should have a
barbecue here tonight.
[SAKURA] Yay! It's been a while
since we've had meat!
[SHIZUKO] Yaaay!
[GIRL B]
That temple food is so light,
it's like eating nothing, huh?
[GIRL C]
After all the walking I could
use some real food for a change!
[BOY B]
Hey you guys what's that?
[BOY C]
Is that paradise I see?
(GIRLS giggling and chattering)
[GIRLS]
Uh? Oh? Huh?
[MISAKI]
What do you think
you're doing? Hey!
Get back in line!
Stay back or else!
[SAKURA]
It's just like all
the seniors told us!
[MISAKI]
What do you mean, Sakura?
After three days of nonstop
meditation, lecturing,
and cleaning at the temple,
combined with a lack of food
and lack of sleep...
[SAKURA]
The guys are stretched so thin
that on the fourth day,
when they're finally free
from the temple, they snap
and lose all reason!
[SAKURA]
They're going to start attacking
the girls!
[MISAKI] Run for it!
(GIRLS screaming)
[GIRL A]
Any other time they barely
pay attention to us!
[SHIZUKO] But at this moment, it
seems that any girl will do.
[SAKURA] This's the worst!
[COACH A]
Attention girls,
escape to the cottage!
[COACH B]
They're rampaging faster
than last year.
[COACH C]
Get a hold of yourselves!
[GIRL A] I've never seen the
boys like that before!
[GIRL B] That was TERRIBLE!
[SHIZUKO]
I'd heard that in the past,
after three days of doing
nothing but temple work,
the girls are completely
unprepared to deal
with the situation...
[MISAKI]
So does that mean the same
thing happens every year?
[SHIZUKO]
Indeed‐ and every year, the
teachers create a barricade
to separate the boys
from the girls.
[SHIZUKO]
That's the only thing that's
kept the girls safe every year.
[SHIZUKO] We'll be fine so long
as the boys can't get through‐
[GIRL D] This is bad!
[GIRL D]
All the rain has flooded the
lake next to the camp,
so the teachers can't
build the barrier!
[SAKURA]
So does that mean...
that... right now the
boys are running loose?
[MISAKI]
What?!
[SHIROKAWA]
I'm so hungry...
[SHINTANI]
Takumi, don't you have
somethin' to eat?
[SHINTANI] Chomp! (chewing)
[SARASHINA]
Tonight's the barbecue, right?
They should've gotten
everything ready by now...
[KUROSAKI]
And it looks like the teachers
still aren't back yet.
[SHIROKAWA]
Okay! How 'bout we head out and
be the first in line for food!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
[KUROSAKI]
You guys coming or not?
[BOY B]
Nah. We're way too restless to
worry
about our empty
stomachs right now.
(BOYS howling)
[BOY C] It's strange. Things
were so peaceful at the
temple...
[BOY F]
Oh, yeah! If we're not doing
anything, the girls must be
free, too!
[GIRLS] Squee!
[BOY E] Girls...
[BOY F]
Free...
[BOY B]
I bet they're soaking wet
after all that rain.
[BOY C]
Oh, yeah? We can't have that.
[BOY B]
Let's go and see 'em right now!
(howling continues)
[MISAKI] Guh!
[GIRL A] I just felt
a terrible chill!
[GIRL B] Me too!
[SAKURA]
Misaki, are you really going?
[MISAKI]
Yeah. If the teachers
are in trouble,
it's the student council's
responsibility to help them
however they can.
[SHIZUKO]
But what about the boys?
[MISAKI]
Listen up, everyone! If the boys
make it this far,
you must fight them off at
all costs, alright, ladies?!
[GIRLS] (scared gasps)
[MISAKI]
So they really came. Hope
they're prepared to meet
their maker!
[SHINTANI]
Huh? That you, Misaki?
[MISAKI]
Gah! What are you doing
here, Shintani?!
[SHINTANI]
Well, everyone kept sayin they
were gonna go see the girls.
[SHINTANI]
And then I thought, I'd sure
like to see you, too!
[SHINTANI]
It seemed, like, a lot of fun
so I thought I'd go and tag
along with'em.
[SHINTANI]
Sneakin' out under the teachers'
noses, hanging out and playin'
cards with the girls...
[MISAKI] Shintani...
[SHINTANI] Huh?
Do these guys look like they've
come all the way over here for a
game of cards?
[SHINTANI] Huh?
[BOY B] Aren't you the
sharp one, President.
[SHINTANI] Oh?
[BOY C] All right men, charge!
(battle cries)
(fighting commences)
[SHINTANI]
What're you... DOINNN'?!
I won't let anyone rough up
my Misaki, you hear me?!
[SHINTANI]
Get yer hands offa her!
[MISAKI]
Who are you calling "my Misaki"?
Just LOOK you moron!
[MISAKI]
These guys aren't in
their right minds!
[MISAKI]
If we let them get past us, it
will only end with the girls in
tears!
[BOY D] Don't worry, President!
[BOY E] We just wanna play
with them! Ah!
[MISAKI] No wait!
[BOYS] (crazed calls)
[USUI]
What's this? A game of tag?
[USUI] Let me play, too.
[MISAKI] Usui!
[USUI]
(snicker) Looks like... I'm
"it." Better start running, or
I'm gonna get you.
[BOY C] H‐Hey!
[BOY D] We're in big
trouble now, aren't we?
[MISAKI]
Usui... Heh
All right! Guess, I'll be "it,"
too!
[SHINTANI]
Hey, me, too! Me, too!
[USUI]
All right, then.
Let's get started.
[BOY C]
We can play next time!
[BOY D]
And with friendly rules!
[SHINTANI]
I thought this was supposed to
be tag.
How come they ain't chasing us?
What're they running off for?
[MISAKI]
That's okay. After all, we
wanted to chase THEM off,
didn't we?
[USUI]
So the "its" win?
[MISAKI] Oh yeah! We sure do!
[USUI] Heh.
[SHINTANI]
Those guys' attitudes really
changed when you showed up,
Takumi.
[MISAKI]
Well, that's because the other
guys know better than to mess
with Usui.
[SHINTANI]
Yeah. I've gotten to know that
all too well during this little
field trip of ours.
[SHINTANI]
Takumi... You're an awesome guy.
[USUI]
In what way?
[SHINTANI]
Whaddya mean "in what way"!
In different ways! Anyway,
I just think you're really
awesome!
[USUI]
Your vocabulary is rather
diminutive isn't it, Sanshita?
[SHINTANI]
Don't call me "Sanshita"!
And don't use hard words!
[USUI] You're kind of an idiot
aren't you Sanshita?
[SHINTANI] Wha?!
(MISAKI laughing)
[USUI] What?
[MISAKI]
(laughing) No, it's nothing,
don't mind me.
[SHIROKAWA]
Everything's been eaten!
[KUROSAKI]
Who could've done such a thing?!
[SARASHINA]
Is this a...
[KUROSAKI]
A bread crust!
[SHIROKAWA]
It was HIM!
[TRIO]
NOOOOO!
[MISAKI]
In the end, the boys and the
girls had separate barbecues,
and once the rain died down,
the teachers hurriedly
constructed the barricade.
And so the girls were able
to eat in complete safety.
[GIRL A]
Are you okay, Misaki?!
[GIRL B]
We were so worried about you!
[SAKURA]
You took so long!
[SHIZUKO]
I'm glad you're all right!
[GIRL C]
Oh Misaki!
[MISAKI]
What the? You're still here?
[USUI]
Yeah, looks like it. Could
you... come with me for a bit?
[USUI]
"These two do nothing but fight.
But they seem to get along well.
Giggle."
[USUI]
That's what you
thought, wasn't it?
What the heck is with you? I
told you not to worry about it.
Yeah, HE tried to dodge the
subject like that, too.
[MISAKI] Uh... da.
[USUI]
Look...
Just tell me one thing,
Ayuzawa... is he special to you?
[MISAKI]
Uh... I‐it's not that
he's "special"...
[MISAKI]
He's a childhood friend,
so I've known him longer
than anyone else, but...
[USUI]
Is that why you're always
watching him all the time?
[MISAKI]
Uh? What are you talking about?!
[USUI]
Oh? Isn't that how it's been
since he's shown up?
You've been worrying about
him since the first time he
arrived.
[MISAKI]
Of course I worry about him!
He's an idiot who's always
getting himself into trouble.
And he's difficult
to deal with! But...
[MISAKI]
You're even MORE difficult...
stupid Usui.
[MISAKI]
Hey! (struggling)
Hey, Usui!
[USUI]
I've reached my limit.
I wasted all my energy...
worrying about that guy.
[MISAKI]
Uh... (awkward laugh)
[USUI]
Mind telling me what's so funny?
[MISAKI]
It's just, the boys are
barbecuing right now.
If you're hungry,
just hurry up and‐
[USUI]
It's no good. I can't move.
[MISAKI]
Oh. It's stopped raining.
[USUI]
Yeah...
[SARASHINA]
Dammit! That bottomless pit
Shintani even ate all the raw
meat!
[SHIROKAWA]
Hey, there's a delicious‐looking
lamb over there...
[KUROSAKI]
And it's a girl too...
[YUKIMURA]
(sleepily) Save me, Mommy...
[KUROSAKI]
The training at the temple is
quite strict, isn't it?
[SHIROKAWA]
Let us be grateful for the food
we receive.
[SARASHINA]
Aah, I'm so grateful
for the sun's embrace!
[MISAKI]
You three idiots are depressing
even in your "enlightened"
state.
[USUI]
Next year, the seniors will lie
to the juniors again, won't
they?
[SATSUKI]
All right! After having
such a horrible experience
at the temple,
how about you eat something
that starts with an "s"?
[MISAKI] Sushi?
[SHINTANI] Steak? Sour pickles?
Salad? Sukiyaki? Suddon
noodles?!
[SATSUKI]
Nope, all wrong. The thing
starting with "s" is "sweets"!
[MISAKI]
I think there's something like
that going on at Maid Latte.
[USUI]
A "challenge" event to eat
a full course of them, Misa.
[SHINTANI]
Whoa, somethin' sure
smells sweet, huh?