(GIRLS in awe)
[GIRL A]
Hey, did you see that guy?
[GIRL B]
Sure did! He was super cute,
wasn't he?
[GIRL C]
That uniform was for Seika
High, right?
[SARASHINA]
Hey, Kurotatsu! Is that a Misa
charm I see on your bag?
[KUROSAKI]
You bet it is‐ handmade
by yours truly!
[SHIROKAWA]
Whoa! I can't tell if I'm
impressed or creeped out! Make
one for me, too.
[KUROSAKI]
Leave it to me! But you've gotta
keep it hidden at school!
[SARASHINA]
Yeah, we know!
[SHIROKAWA]
It would be bad if anyone saw.
[TRIO]
Yahoo!
[GIRL A] Soooo... my lunch
box looks like it only has
3 trays‐ but it really has 6!
[GIRL B] My repertoire of
impersonations has expanded
dramatically!
[GIRL C]
CBS acquired the Fender
companies in 1965, didn't they?
[SHINTANI]
Hmm... Hmph.
[MISAKI]
You will clean out your
clubrooms and that's final!
[BOYS] Whoa!
[BOY A]
But Miss President,
you can't suddenly...
[MISAKI]
There's nothing "sudden" about
it! I've been telling you to
clean them for weeks!
And yet... what the hell is
this?! The club building smells
so funky that it's starting to
give off an evil aura!
(BOYS complaining)
[BOY A] What are
you talking about!?
[BOY B] We don't see anything!
[MISAKI]
That's because you pigs roll
around in this stench day in
and day out!
[BOYS] Huh? (back
to complaining)
[BOY B] Who cares about some
stupid smelly aura?
[MISAKI]
Ungh! Enough arguing‐ everyone
will come in tomorrow to clean.
[BOY C]
There's no way we can
finish in one day!
[BOY A]
We're probably gonna have to
stay super late to get all
of it done.
[BOY B]
You won't even give us any
time to eat, will you? Slave
driver...
[YUKIMURA] Excuse me, everyone?
[ALL] Huh?
[YUKIMURA]
I'll make sure to prepare enough
snacks for everyone.
So won't you please take
care of the cleaning?
[YUKIMURA]
I can make rice balls...
[MISAKI]
Yukimura! Where did YOU come
from?
[YUKIMURA]
They surrounded you, and I just
panicked... I'm sorry!
[MISAKI]
Well, thanks to you, it looks
like this cleaning will actually
happen.
[YUKIMURA]
But now that I think about it,
how am I going to make enough
snacks for all of those people?!
[KANOU]
In such a short amount of
time, it's impossible.
[YUKIMURA]
Don't say that, Kanou, what am I
going to do?! (sobbing)
[KANOU]
Well, don't cry about it.
Everyone on the student council
will pitch in and make it work
somehow.
After all, it was the council
that requested the buildings be
cleaned in the first place.
[YUKIMURA]
I will put my heart and soul
into making these rice balls!
[MISAKI]
I wonder if those guys will be
okay with one per person...?
[KANOU]
They definitely will not.
[YUKIMURA]
Mr. Usui! Aha... It's been so
long! You've been absent for a
while now, haven't you?
[USUI]
Yeah. I got a little hurt.
[YUKIMURA] Wha!
[USUI]
It's been awhile...
Miss President.
[MISAKI]
Are you all better now?
[USUI] Thanks to you I am.
[KANOU] Uh?
[MISAKI]
I'm sure you're glad to be back.
Let's go, Yukimura.
[YUKIMURA]
Uh, um... Wait,
Miss President!
[YUKIMURA]
Oh, by the way, Mr. Usui.
If you had to pick your
favorite food to snack on,
what would it be?
Rice soup.
[MISAKI] Ulp!
[KANOU] Huh?
[YUKIMURA]
No, um, I mean more like
the kind of snack you'd enjoy
after doing a lot of hard work.
[USUI] What's wrong
with rice soup?
[YUKIMURA] Huh?!
But why rice soup?!
[MAN]
Well, if you need anything
you just let me know.
[MISAKI]
Excuse me, sir.
[MAN]
Ah...
[MISAKI]
Yes?
[MAN]
Let's just wait till Monday.
[MISAKI]
Actually, I have something to
ask about tomorrow's campus
cleanup.
[MAN] Ugh...
[MISAKI] I'd like to provide
some snacks for the club
members.
[YUKIMURA]
Kanou! I'll be running late
tonight, so would you go on
ahead?
[KANOU]
Understood, sir.
[BOY]
Mr. Vice President, a moment!
[YUKIMURA]
See you later, Kanou!
[MISAKI]
You two have become great
friends, haven't you?
[KANOU]
And you, President...
You two have become a great
couple, haven't you?
[MISAKI]
Huh? What are you talking about?
[KANOU]
I don't really understand what
you're trying to hide it for.
[MISAKI]
Seriously, what are
you talking about?
[KANOU]
You and Usui‐ you're dating
aren't you? ARGH!
[MISAKI] Are you an idiot?!
[KANOU] (struggling)
[MISAKI]
You've gotta be kidding me! Who
would date a perverted weirdo
like him?!
[KANOU]
But why did you look after him
and make him rice soup if you're
not his girlfriend?!
(MISAKI gasps)
[MISAKI]
How‐ How did you know...?
[KANOU]
I'm sorry. I could
just tell somehow.
[MISAKI]
(breath) That was because...
I owed him a lot of favors and
I had to pay him back somehow.
[MISAKI]
I couldn't help it. So don't go
getting the wrong idea!
[KANOU]
I... I'm sorry I asked.
So, you have another one...
a love letter, I mean...
[USUI] Aah, what a headache.
Will you go for me?
[KANOU] Huh?
She said she's waiting in the
second‐years' classroom.
[KANOU]
I can't go in your place!
[USUI]
What, you're saying you're
still scared of girls?
[KANOU]
That's not the problem
here and you know it!
[USUI]
You're kinda useless,
aren't you, Kanou?
[KANOU] Wha?!
[USUI] Fine, then throw this
garbage away.
[KANOU] Huh?
[USUI]
Calm down‐ I was just kidding.
[KANOU]
Then why don't you just
go out with someone?
[KANOU]
If it's such a "headache,"
why not properly date someone?
[KANOU]
There'd probably be fewer of
these confessions. And also...
[KANOU]
It looks like President Ayuzawa
hasn't noticed how much you... I
mean...
[USUI]
You sure are awfully talkative
today, aren't you, Kanou?
[KANOU] Huh?
[USUI]
Does seeing this make you
annoyed? Frustrated?
[KANOU]
Uh, no, that's not what I am
saying, I just‐
[USUI]
Look, I'm not angry
about it, you know.
[KANOU]
Eh? I see...
[USUI] I'm just sick of it...
all of that stuff.
(KANOU groaning)
[USUI]
Trying to date someone
"properly" is an even...
bigger headache.
[KANOU]
A "headache"... huh...
[MAIDS]
Thank you for coming, Master!
[SATSUKI]
What are you doing here, Aoi?
And why are you wearing one of
our uniforms again?
[AOI] What's the big deal‐ the
shop's already closed...
[HONOKA] I told you, I was
supposed to be the one in the
middle!
[SATSUKI] Hurry up and
go home, middle‐schooler!
[AOI] Hey! Let go of me!
[ERIKA]
Well, guess it's time for us to
head home, too.
[SUBARU]
Should we go get something to
eat?
[HONOKA]
Can I come with you guys, too?
[SUBARU] Of course!
[ERIKA] Do you know
anywhere good?
[BOTH]
We're the kitchen sisters!
[SEN‐CHAN]
We didn't have as many orders
for rice dishes today
as we thought we would, so
we have a lot of extra rice.
[MOCCHI]
We made rice balls with the
leftovers‐ why don't we all eat
them together?
[SUBARU]
Well, it looks like we'll be
dining at Maid Latte tonight.
[ERIKA]
It certainly is cheaper.
[HONOKA]
Yeah, that's for sure.
[SATSUKI]
Too bad Misa's not here‐
I could've given her
some to take home.
[AOI]
Mmm, Tasty.
[MISAKI]
(strained) Come on! Just
turn into a triangle already!
[USUI]
Rice Soup.
[MISAKI]
No, no! I can't get
distracted! (determined)
[MISAKI]
If I... just squeeze it
tighter... it should work!
[SUZUNA]
Hey Sis. What are
you doing in here?
[MISAKI]
Oh nothing... just practicing
how to make rice balls.
[MISAKI]
What the‐?!
I can't waste any more rice...
[MISAKI] Guuuuhhhh...
[SUZUNA]
Hey... I know...
[MISAKI] Huh?
[SUZUNA] Then why
don't you try this?
Mix tiny balls of tissue in
with the rest of the rice.
[MISAKI]
Whoa! Great idea, Suzuna! Being
poor sure makes you creative.
[MISAKI]
All right! Now I can go on a
rice ball‐making rampage!
[SUZUNA]
Please don't burn
the house down.
[MISAKI]
Okay! Now to begin making them
for real!
[YUKIMURA]
Miss President, you're not
looking too well. Did you sleep
okay?
[MISAKI]
I‐it's nothing at all!
I'm fine‐ really!
[MISAKI, thinking]
I've got this. I finally got
the shape down this morning.
I can definitely make these!
[MISAKI]
All right, everyone! We've got
some rice balls to make!
[YUKIMURA]
Oh! Miss President, it looks
like we have another helper!
[KANOU]
Yes... I'm available...
[MISAKI]
O‐oh great. Thank you...
[KANOU]
I haven't seen Usui at all
today, is he here?
[YUKIMURA]
Um... Now that you mention it,
he hasn't shown up today.
[KANOU]
Tell me, Yukimura... what do you
think about Usui and President
Ayuzawa.
[YUKIMURA]
I think they're great people.
[KANOU]
That's not exactly what I meant.
[YUKIMURA]
Ouch! What do you mean then,
about them?
[KANOU]
I mean... what do you think
about their relationship?
[YUKIMURA] Oh...
[USUI] Bwsh!
[MISAKI] Flash!
[YUKIMURA]
They're a golden combination!
[KANOU]
A what now?!
[YUKIMURA]
They're both incredible.
They're good at
everything they do.
Sometimes, it seems like
they're on a totally different
level than everyone else.
[YUKIMURA]
It's like they're part of a
world someone like me could
never enter.
[YUKIMURA]
Miss President... is always
having to come to my rescue.
[YUKIMURA]
If I could just be a little more
like Mr. Usui, I could be more
helpful to her.
[KANOU]
Huh? Yukimura... do you like
President Ayuzawa?
Yup. I like her very much.
[KANOU]
(sigh) That's quite the
confession...
[YUKIMURA]
No! Wait a minute! I didn't mean
it like THAT!
I don't "LIKE her" like her!
[MISAKI]
Dammit, Yukimura! What are you
blabbering about?
Less talking, more rice‐balling!
[YUKIMURA]
Y‐yes, ma'am!
[BOY]
I'm tired of waiting all day...
This is too much work.
[BOY] We're outta here!
[SHINTANI]
(sniff) (chomp) I ain't been
eating enough vegetables lately.
[USUI] Huh?
[MISAKI]
And... Finished!
Good job, everyone! You all made
some great rice balls!
[KANOU]
Huh? What's with these deformed
ones over here?
[ALL]
(freaking out)
Wait! Those are...!
[MISAKI] They're OBVIOUSLY rice
balls, Kanou.
[KANOU] (scared) HUH!
[MISAKI]
Can't you tell just by looking
at them?!
[KANOU] Eh? B‐But they
don't look like‐
[MISAKI] Then try eating one!
[MISAKI] See, it's a rice ball!
It's just a little salty!
[KANOU] But, they're
making a disturbing sound!
[MISAKI] You're hearing things.
[BOYS]
WHERE THE SNACKS AT?!
[MISAKI]
Hey, you guys‐! AHHH!
[BOY A]
They're ready!
[BOYS]
(frantic eating)
[MISAKI]
(struggling) Hey, hey! What are
you...? Have you even done any
cleaning yet?
[BOY B] What are these things?
[BOY A] There are some weird
balls mixed in here.
[BOY C]
Let's toss 'em.
[SHINTANI]
Gwah!
[KANAGAWA]
Hey, this is bad.
[YUKIMURA]
It's getting completely
out of control!
[MISAKI]
I hope you morons are
prepared...
[MISAKI]
BECAUSE I'M ABOUT
TO BRING THE PAIN!
(BOYS screaming)
[BOY B] Somebody save us!
[MISAKI]
Gleam!
Stomp. Stomp. Stomp. Stomp.
[KANAGAWA]
Well, I guess it was...
nice knowing them...
[YUKIMURA]
There's nothing we can do for
them now‐ let's finish cleaning
things up.
[SHINTANI]
Ow...
[SHINTANI] FOOD!
[SHIROKAWA]
We got Misa's rice balls!
[SARASHINA] Such treasures!
[KUROSAKI] They're incredible!
[SHIROKAWA] Such treasures.
[SARASHINA] I'll cherish this
for the rest of my life!
[KUROSAKI]
What do you think
they're made of?
[MISAKI]
Hm? Those guys...
They cleaned up everything
before they went home.
[MISAKI]
If they were going to clean,
couldn't they have at least
thrown these away, too?
Ugh! These are pretty terrible.
So much for staying up
all night to make them...
Even that rice soup I
made before is better
than these things.
(sigh) There's no way that he
would ever want to eat something
like this monstrosity.
(yawn) I'm so tired...
[USUI]
(snorting) How did she even
make these? (chuckles)
[USUI]
Well... at least you gave it
your all, right Ayuzawa?
[USUI]
Good work today.
[YUKIMURA]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I brought our bags, too!
[KANOU] I really don't
understand them at all.
[YUKIMURA] Huh?
[KANOU]
How can they care so much for
each other and yet never tell
each other how they feel?
[KANOU]
Why do they avoid it...
instead of trying
to move forward?
[YUKIMURA]
What are you grumbling about?
[MISAKI, thinking]
When I woke up yesterday, all of
those rice ball rejects were
gone...I wonder where they went?
[MISAKI, thinking]
Talk about strange...
[USUI] Miss President.
[MISAKI]
Gah! Wh‐Why are you always
popping up out of thin
air like that?!
[USUI] Huh? Really? I thought I
appeared pretty normally.
[MISAKI] The hell you did!
[USUI]
Come on, it's not like I fell
out of the sky or something.
[MISAKI] Duh, stupid!
[SHINTANI] (chomp)
[MISAKI]
People don't just fall
out of the sky‐!
[SHINTANI]
(munching) Aah, thank goodness.
I can't believe I almost dropped
my precious food like that!
(MISAKI stunned)
[SHINTANI] Yeah, that sure was
clumsy of me.
[HOMEROOM TEACHER] Class, this
is Hinata Shintani, a transfer
student.
[MISAKI] Uh?
[HOMEROOM TEACHER]
He was born here, but moved to
Kyushu for about 10... Eh?
What's the matter?
[BOY D]
Uh? What's your problem, man?
[SHINTANI]
(sniff) I smell honey and lemon.
[BOY D]
Ah? You mean...
this?
[SHINTANI] Ahhhhh!
[BOY I] He looks
like he wants it.
[BOY J] He REALLY looks
[BOY D]
Here, take it dude. Just quit
staring at me like that, ya
weirdo.
Huh? You really mean it?! You're
a stand‐up guy, you know that!
Don't mind if I do‐
[HOMEROOM TEACHER]
Hey, Shintani! You can't eat
in homeroom... you... know...
[BOYS] He looks sad.
[BOY J] He looks REALLY sad.
[SHINTANI]
I can't?
[HOMEROOM TEACHER]
Um, well, maybe... just this
once...
[MISAKI]
Of course you can't keep it!
Sir, you can't baby him right
off that like this!
[MISAKI]
He has to be held to the same
standard as everyone else.
[HOMEROOM TEACHER]
Yes, ah, you're right.
[MISAKI]
It was "Shintani"... wasn't it?
Please put that candy away now.
[SHINTANI]
You big meanie! Wahhh!
[MISAKI] Hey now! What're you
getting so worked up for? And
you guys, keep it down!
[MISAKI]
And, over here is the gym.
(SHINTANI munching)
[MISAKI]
Hey! How many times do
I have to tell you?
Quit eating while you're
walking, it's rude!
[SHINTANI]
I can't help it. I'm
hungry so I gotta eat.
[MISAKI] Confiscated!
[SHINTANI] Huh? No!
[MISAKI] Don't "no" me, mister!
[SHINTANI] But those are
mine! (sobbing)
[KOSUGI] Miss President, sorry
to bother you.
[KOSUGI]
Could you please take a look
at the handouts for today's
meeting?
[MISAKI]
Oh, sure thing.
These bread crusts are coming
with me!
[SHINTANI]
Idiot! Meanie! (wailing)
[MISAKI]
Is that guy really
a high‐school student?
[SHINTANI]
(sigh)
[BOY D]
Hey, new guy!
[BOY I]
Allow us to introduce
ourselves...
[MISAKI]
Just fix this part right here
and add what I mentioned earlier
and it'll be perfect.
[MISAKI]
And please make enough copies
for everyone, okay?
[USUI]
You sure have been spending a
lot of time with that transfer
student, Miss President.
[USUI]
You're not paying any attention
to me at all. That makes me feel
lonely.
[MISAKI]
You liar! You don't look
"lonely" at all.
[MISAKI]
You haven't even been showing
yourself all day.
[USUI]
Oh? But I've been watching you
this whole time, Misa.
[MISAKI]
No surprise there, after all
you're a pervert stalker‐
[USUI]
You saw, didn't you, Ayuzawa?
You saw me.
[USUI]
You saw me, didn't you?
[SAKURA]
There you are, Misaki!
That transfer student's
in trouble!
A bunch of guys have
him surrounded!
[MISAKI]
What?!
[SHIZUKO]
It looked like a dangerous
situation,
so we thought we should
inform you right away.
[MISAKI] Where?
[SAKURA] This way!
[MISAKI]
Over there, huh?
Hey, what are you guys‐?!
[MISAKI]
THIS is a "dangerous situation"?
[SHIZUKO]
No‐ earlier it seemed as if
they were going to break
into a fight at any moment!
[SHINTANI] ahhh....
(BOYS chuckling)
[BOY J]
Hey, it's my turn next‐ try and
guess what I'VE got!
[BOY J]
If you get it right,
I'll give you a reward!
[SHINTANI]
(sniff) (grin) Cheese‐flavored
potato chips!
[BOYS] Whoa!
[BOY J] That's right!
[BOY F]
You're awesome, Shintani!
[SHINTANI]
Reward, reward...!
[BOY G]
How'd you know even though the
bag's not open?
[BOY E]
Dude, I can't believe you eat so
much and don't get fat.
[SHINTANI]
Well, back in the day, I was
SUPER fat!
[SHINTANI]
But when I was in elementary
school, both my parents died in
a car wreck,
and I went to live with
my Grampaw in Kyushu.
[SHINTANI]
It was way out in the country,
with no candy shops around,
so since the only things to eat
were veggies I ended up droppin'
some weight.
[SHINTANI]
But then Gramps said, "All the
fields in the world
ain't enough to feed ya‐
yer gonna eat us straight
out of house an' home!"
[SHINTANI] So I came back here,
where I used to live.
[BOY J] Oh wow, that was an
unexpectedly tragic back story.
[BOY J]
So, you live all by yourself?
[SHINTANI] Yeah.
[BOY I] What about tuition?
[SHINTANI]
I get by on what my folks left
behind for me.
[BOYS]
You've been through so
much, haven't you!
[SHINTANI] Huh? Really?
[BOYS sobbing)
[BOY J]
I thought he was just some idiot
who ate like a pig.
[BOY I]
He's smiling on the outside,
but he's hurting on the inside!
[SHINTANI]
"Hurting"? How come?
It's no biggie. I just came back
to this town so I could find my
first love, that's all, ya see.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SHINTANI]
When I thought about
seeing her again,
I just couldn't control myself!
[BOY I]
But, wait, didn't your grandpa
kick you out?
[SHINTANI]
Well, the thing about Gramps
is...
[SHINTANI]
He said, "I was just pullin'
your leg! Don't leave!" but I
was all,
[SHINTANI]
"Don't worry, Gramps‐ I'll come
back when it looks like you're
gonna die."
[GRANDPA]
I'm more worried
'bout you than me!
[BOY E]
So then you came back just to
see that girl again?
[SHINTANI]
Yup! From here on out I'll be
searching for her high an'low,
day‐in an' day‐out!
[SHINTANI]
She was so kind and happy, and
she looked after me tenderly...
[SHINTANI]
Yeah! She's like a single,
lovely flower bloomin' in the
fields...
[SHINTANI]
Aah, how I long for you to feed
me sweet cake once again...!
[SHINTANI] Just wait, My
Darling! I'll find you!
[MISAKI] Hold it, Shintani!
[MISAKI]
Does that girl even go to this
school?
[SHINTANI]
Dunno.
[MISAKI]
Ack! You don't know?!
Then how exactly do you plan to
find her?!
No idea. But that girl...
I made her a promise...
I promised to stay by
Misaki's side no matter what.
[SAKURA]
Did he... just say "Misaki"?
[BOY J]
(chuckling) Dude, it's supposed
to be the other way around!
[BOY I]
Any guy promising to stick by a
girl? You sure are one hopeless
guy aren't you?
[SHINTANI]
But that's the promise I made.
[BOY H]
Hang on... I think I've heard
the name "Misaki" somewhere
before...
(YOUNG SHINTANI straining)
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Hey, that's dangerous!
[YOUNG SHINTANI] Ahhhh!
[YOUNG MISAKI] Oh?
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Geez, I told you not to climb up
that far, Yoh.
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Here. Say "Aah," 'kay?
Don't go running off climbing
trees anymore.
You have to promise to stay
by side from now on, okay?
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
Okay, Misaki. I promise.
I'll stay by you forever and
ever no matter what.
[MISAKI] (horrific realization)
[SAKURA] Say, Misaki...
[SAKURA]
Are you the same "Misaki" that
boy's been talking about?
[SHIZUKO]
Surely he would've
noticed by now?
[SHIZUKO] After all the time
they've spent talking
you would think he would
have recognized her at
least to some degree...
[MISAKI] Hinata... Yohkoh...
[BOTH] Huh?
[MISAKI]
When I was in elementary school,
there was a boy in my class with
the nickname "Yohkoh"...
[MISAKI]
...because his name could be
read that way, too.
[MISAKI]
That kid was always eating, and
he was also a little on the
chunky side.
[SAKURA] Huh?! Then...
[SHIZUKO] Then that means
that boy's first love was...!
[MISAKI]
Probably me.
[SAKURA] Does that mean you and
Hinata used to date?!
[MISAKI] Huh?!
[SAKURA]
(squeal) What an
exciting turn of events!
[MISAKI]
What makes you say that?!
[BOY H] Awesome!
[BOY J] You all right, Hinata?
[MISAKI] That idiot!
[SHINTANI]
Whoa... I can see the entire
campus from up here.
[SHINTANI]
Okay...
Oh, Misa! Come out come out
wherever you are!
[BOY I, chuckling] Oh boy,
there he goes.
[BOY H] That's hilarious.
[BOY J] He's the best!
[SHINTANI] Hey Misaki!
[MISAKI] This is no time
for laughing!
[MISAKI]
Hurry up and get down
from there, Shintani!
Up here I won't be bothered
by a certain MEANIE!
[SHINTANI]
Hey! Misakiiiii! Where are you!
[MISAKI]
Don't come cryin' to me
if you fall again!
[MISAKI] Dammit!
He's ignoring me?!
[SHINTANI] Misaki!
[MISAKI] Hey, Shintani, If you
don't get down here right now
I'm taking your candy, your
snacks, AND your bread crusts!
[SHINTANI] Heeeey!
[SHINTANI] Wah!
(MISAKI gasps)
(SHINTANI yelling)
[MISAKI]
Yoh...
Yoh!
[SHINTANI]
You there... What's your name?
[MISAKI]
Misaki... Ayuzawa.
Sorry, but I'm a lot different
from how I used to‐ uh?
[SHINTANI] Misa!
[SHINTANI]
I missed you so much!
[BOYS]
HUH?
[MISAKI] I never thought that
Shintani the transfer student
would end up being Yoh!
[USUI] Hrm...
[MISAKI] What is it, Usui? Is
there something you want to say?
[USUI] Hrm...
[SHINTANI]
Misa! Bread crusts are good when
they're fried
[SHINTANI]
and dusted with sugar, but
they're even better plain!
[MISAKI] Where did you get those
bread crusts from?! Confiscated!
[SHINTANI] Misaki, you're so
cruel!
[MISAKI]
Why do I get the feeling he was
trying to get those confiscated
on purpose?
[SAKURA] Maybe he just wanted to
get your attention!
[SHIZUKO] Mhm...
[MISAKI] Sakura and Shizuko!
[SAKURA]
So, next time we're gonna go
into the forest with the new
transfer student!
[SHIZUKO]
Apparently, we're going
to a mountain temple.
[USUI]
Hrm...?