[MINAKO] Oh, wait!
[MINAKO] C'mon, quit trying to
get away.
[USUI] There's one over here,
too.
[MINAKO] Oh my, you're right.
Thank you for being so kind.
[MINAKO] I'm sorry for having to
trouble you like this...
[USUI] It's fine.
[MINAKO] Your uniform...
You're a Seika student, aren't
you?
[MINAKO] I'm glad! Even though
the school has a bad reputation,
it does have its good students.
[USUI] Ah...
Actually, my daughter
happens to go there, too.
[MINAKO] But she's so focused on
her schoolwork
that she doesn't seem to
make a lot of friends,
especially with boys.
[MINAKO] I used to worry about
her all the time.
I wasn't sure if she'd really be
able to enjoy high school to the
fullest.
And when she's not at school,
she's either studying or
working.
Aren't normal high school girls
supposed to have fun and fall in
love?
They get all dolled up and
go on dates and things?
[USUI] Uh... Yeah I guess.
[MINAKO] I guess I'm the one to
blame, though,
I haven't exactly made her life
easy...
[MINAKO] But now I feel much
more relieved.
I'm really glad I ran into you.
Because you seem like a very
kind young man.
Recently, she does seem like
she's become more like a normal
high school girl.
[MINAKO] I'm sure it's because
she's made friends with someone
nice like you.
[USUI] Um... has anyone ever
referred to your daughter as
"unreserved"?
Oh?
[MINAKO] Why yes, all the time.
You're quite perceptive.
[MINAKO] Thank you again.
you've really been a big help.
[USUI] I had a feeling this was
gonna happen,
but I can't believe I was right.
[MINAKO] Please, come on in!
[USUI] I'll be on my way then...
[MINAKO] Oh, please wait!
At least let me make
you some tea.
[SUZUNA] Mom, did you fall in
the hole again?
[SUZUNA] Oh. Did you come to fix
the floor?
[SUZUNA] Please help yourself.
[MINAKO] Sorry for all the
trouble I've put you through‐
I even had to ask you to fix our
floor!
[USUI] It's fine.
[SUZUNA] Still, he did such a
good job
that now that's the safest spot
in the entire house.
[MINAKO] True enough. Won't you
have one, Usui?
[USUI] Yeah.
[SUZUNA] But Mom, you have to be
more careful
and watch your step so we don't
make any more holes.
[MINAKO] Yes, it's gotten pretty
dangerous, hasn't it?
[MISAKI] I'm home!
[MISAKI] Huh?
[MISAKI] Someone replaced the
floor boards...
[MISAKI] Who fixed up the
hallway all nice and...
[MISAKI] Gah!
[MINAKO] Welcome back, Misaki.
[SUZUNA] Welcome back, Sis.
[USUI] Welcome back, Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI] Usui?! Why are you in
my house?
[USUI] Crunch, crunch, crunch.
[USUI] It's kind of a long
story.
[MISAKI] Just spit it out
already!
[MINAKO] Oh, my! What
coincidence‐
so the two of you happen to be
friends after all.
[SUZUNA] I think you've got it
wrong, Mom.
[MINAKO] I invited him to come
in for a bit.
[MINAKO] He helped me carry my
apples after they spilled out
all over the road.
[MINAKO] He even fixed the holes
in the hallway for us.
[MISAKI] You're plotting
something aren't you?
[USUI] Oh no, you caught me.
[SUZUNA] Sis, you really...
don't trust guys at all, do you?
[MISAKI] What?!
Yes, that certainly seems
to be the case, doesn't it?
[SUZUNA] After all, it's hard to
trust another man
when your father runs out on you
like ours did.
[MISAKI] Don't just casually say
something like that
in front of a stranger!
And you, that's nothing
to laugh about!
Enough, just get outta here.
[USUI] Sorry for the bother.
Oh, Usui, you're leaving
already?
[SUZUNA] See you next time.
[MISAKI] Hurry up now! Come on!
[SAKURA] Huuuh? Hey wait a
second. Was that Misaki and
Usui?
[SHIZUKO] Yes, I believe it was.
[SAKURA] Am I going crazy
or did they just come out of
Misaki's house together?!
[SHIZUKO] Furthermore, if my
eyes did not deceive me,
they were also holding hands.
[SAKURA] We've gotta follow
them!
[SHIZUKO] Unfortunately...
It would appear we've
already lost them.
[SAKURA] Aw, they got away...
[MISAKI] I dragged Usui along
and now we ended up here...
[USUI] Picking up those apples
from the road
and "accidentally" bumping into
your mom...
[USUI] You think I planned that
whole thing, don't you?
[MISAKI] It's true that my mom's
pretty gullible, but even so...
[MISAKI] You're not the type of
guy
that'd take advantage of someone
like that.
[MISAKI] Thank you. For giving
my mom a hand.
[USUI] You're quite welcome.
[LITTLE GIRL A] Here, it's a
chocolate.
[LITTLE GIRL B] Nuh‐uh!
[USUI] Still, the atmosphere
in your house is refreshing.
[MISAKI] What does that mean?
[USUI] It's helped me
understand some things.
[MISAKI] H‐hey, what's that
smirk about?!
[MISAKI] Don't think this means
you've got something you can use
against me.
[MISAKI] I'm not ashamed that my
dad disappeared without a trace
or that our house is in
shambles!
[USUI] That's not what I meant.
What's with those apple slices?
Do you always peel them in the
shape of a rabbit,
or do you only do it for special
guests?
[MISAKI] Mom's always made those
like that since we were kids‐
they were Suzuna's favorite
snack.
[USUI] I also saw where your
heights were marked on the wall.
[MISAKI] You saw that?!
[USUI] I bet you were a cute
kid, too.
Probably even cuter than you are
now.
[USUI] I want so many more
secrets, ones about you that
only I know.
[MISAKI] One secret is more than
enough!
And don't ever come by my house
again‐ got it?!
You're banned from the premises!
[USUI] Whaaat?
[SAKURA] Misaki! Good morninggg!
[SHIZUKO] Good morning, Misaki.
[MISAKI] Oh, good morning.
[SAKURA] Misaki, I swear!
You didn't have to hide it from
us!
[MISAKI] Huh? What are you
talking about?
[SAKURA] Don't play dumb with
me, silly!
We totally saw you and Usui
walking out of your house
together yesterday.
[SHIZUKO] And you were holding
hands.
[SAKURA] VERY tightly!
[MISAKI] You guys saw that?!
[SAKURA] If you're going out,
you're going out. You should've
told us!
[SAKURA] We're friends, right?
Hmph!
[MISAKI] H‐hold on a second!
You've got the wrong idea!
[MISAKI] Usui ran into my mom
and helped her out, so she
invited him INSIDE my house,
[MISAKI] so I was holding his
hand while I was trying to drag
him back out, that's all!
[SHIZUKO] Oh, so that's what it
was.
[SAKURA] What a letdown!
I was so excited about it
that I was up all night long!
[SHIZUKO] It's rather
disappointing.
[SAKURA] So then, you've never
gone over to Usui's or anything
either?
[MISAKI] Nope. I don't even know
his address.
Actually, I don't WANT to know.
[SAKURA] Too bad, I thought you
guys
would make such a good
couple, too...
[SHIZUKO] Now now, it's still
possible
that things will take
an unexpected turn.
[SAKURA] Yeah, there's still
hope!
[SAKURA] But y'know, Usui is
kind of a mystery, huh?
What if he goes to an average
school like Seika
in an attempt to cover up his
secret identity
as the heir to a vast fortune or
something like that?
[MISAKI] No, I can't picture
that at all.
[SAKURA] And every day after
school,
he goes and swims a few laps at
a high‐class sports club,
then goes and gets
fitted in a high‐class,
custom‐tailored suit,
then wears it straight
out of the store
to eat a full‐course
meal at a high‐class restaurant!
[SHIZUKO] I think someone's
allowing her imagination
to get a little too
carried away.
[SAKURA] No, I'm not! It could
totally be true!
[MISAKI] After school,
Usui just goes to Maid Latte
every day...
[MISAKI] Nah, there's no way.
[SAKURA] Hey, why don't we all
go see Usui's house?
[MISAKI] Huh? What for?
[SAKURA] Now I definitely
wanna know what his story is...
[SAKURA] Like what he does when
he's not at school!
You wanna know too, right
Misaki?
[MISAKI] Uh, no,
I'm not really interested.
But first we have to
find a way to get ahold
of his address.
But the school won't just hand
over his contact information
because of the Personal
Information Protection Act or
whatever, so we'll have to hack
into the school's computer and
dive into their secret files and
get it ourselves, all
secret‐like. Shizuko, you're
good with computers, aren't you?
Hack into the mainframe!
That would be a heinous offense.
[SAKURA] Guess that's out.
Well how about we just ask him
directly?
[SAKURA] Go ask him, Misaki.
[MISAKI] I'm telling you,
I'm not interested!
[MISAKI] You know, I am kinda
curious about what Usui's family
is like...
[USUI] Usui's mom.
[USUI] Usui's dad.
[USUI] Usui's younger sister.
[USUI] Usui's baby brother.
[USUI] Takumi is so grateful to‐
[MISAKI] It's no good!
I can't imagine it at all!
Maybe he really is an
alien from another planet.
That would explain a lot.
[MISAKI] Master, do your best!
Why am I even giving it
this much thought?
It must be because of what
Sakura said earlier.
[MISAKI] Oh, my phone.
[MISAKI] Wow, speaking of here
she is.
[MISAKI] Yeah, this is Ayuzawa.
You there Sakura?
[SAKURA] Misaki! We need you to
come here, and fast!
[MISAKI] What's going on?
[SAKURA] Shizuko and I are
tailing Usui.
[MISAKI] No way! Are you
seriously tailing him?!
[SAKURA] He just walked into
some maid coffee shop in the
neighboring town.
[MISAKI] What's he doing in the
neighboring town?
[MISAKI] Wait, THIS is the
neighboring town...
[SAKURA] The shop's name is,
let's see...
[SHIZUKO] Maid Latte!
[SAKURA] Yeah, it's Maid Latte.
Definitely Maid Latte.
Have you heard of it, Misaki?
[SAKURA] Hello? Misaki? Can you
hear me?
[SAKURA] Hello? Misaki? Are you
still there‐
[MISAKI] Yup, he's here all
right.
[MISAKI] And those Three Idiots,
too.
[MISAKI] What should I do?
I haven't told either of them
that I work here...
[MISAKI] I'd have to explain why
Usui and those others guys are
here, too...
That would just suck!
[SATSUKI] Huh? Watcha doin',
Misa?
[SATSUKI] Oh, no! You're
sweating like crazy!
Are you not feeling well today?
[MISAKI] No, it's all right!
This is‐
[SATSUKI] Pushing yourself too
hard like this
is a bad habit of yours, Misa.
Go home and get
plenty of rest today.
[SATSUKI] We have plenty of
coverage so don't worry about
that.
[MISAKI] Okay...
[TRIO] Heave ho! Heave ho!
[SHIROKAWA] The day we've worked
so hard for has finally come!
[SARASHINA] Yeah! Today we're no
longer three broke guys
forced to share a single
Cutesy‐Cutesy Rice Omelette.
[KUROSAKI] We went all out
and ordered the whole menu!
[SHIROKAWA] I bet Misa can't
wait to see us...
[KUROSAKI] Do you think all the
plates'll fit on one table?
[SARASHINA] There's no way they
could!
[HONOKA] Sorry for the wait.
You've ordered one of
everything, is that right?
[TRIO] Yes! Yes, yes, yes!
[HONOKA] Very well then
we'll go ahead and set
everything down.
Please enjoy your meals!
[SHIROKAWA] Excuse me, where's
Misa at?
[HONOKA] I'm sorry, Master,
but it appears that Misa has
today off.
[TRIO] She's off?!
[SHIROKAWA] Then what was the
point of ordering all of this
stuff?!
[SAKURA] Geez, he's been in
there for a long time.
[SHIZUKO] We have to be patient.
[MISAKI] What are you guys
doing?!
[SAKURA] Whoa, that sure was
fast!
[SHIZUKO] Misaki, how were you
able to get here so quickly?
[MISAKI] The more important
question is, why are you
following him?
[SAKURA] We realized that even
if we didn't know his address,
[SAKURA] we should just follow
him back to his house and see
where he lived for ourselves.
[SAKURA] Look, we brought
a disguise for you, too.
[MISAKI] There's no need for
that.
I already told you
I don't WANT to know about
Usui's personal life.
[SAKURA] Now, now, don't be shy!
We know you're curious!
[SAKURA] I can see exactly
what you're thinking, Misaki!
Ha!
[SHIZUKO] Usui is exiting the
store!
[SHIZUKO] He's headed this way.
[MAN B] Sorry, sir, I lost
him.
[MAN A] Oh, well. Just let me
out here.
[MAN B] Okay.
[SHIZUKO] Still, looks can be
quite deceiving, can't they? To
think that Usui would visit a
maid café...
[SAKURA] Maybe he's got a crush
on one of the girls that works
there.
[SAKURA] But I thought
he was interested in YOU,
Misaki.
Geez, what a bummer. Hmph!
[MISAKI] Sakura!
[SAKURA] Hmph! Hmph!
[MISAKI] Look, I really don't
like this.
Let's just stop
before he catches us.
[SHIZUKO] He's on the move!
[SHIZUKO] He entered this
building.
[SHIZUKO] This is...
[SHIZUKO] A high‐class sports
club.
[SAKURA] It's just like I
imagined!
[MISAKI] That's a pretty
straightforward name for a gym.
[SHIZUKO] Let's go.
[SAKURA] Yeah!
[MISAKI] I don't like this.
[SAKURA] Whoa! The inside really
lives up to its name!
[MISAKI] He's been coming to a
place like this?
[SHIZUKO] It seems he got off at
the second floor.
[SAKURA] I knew it! He's
definitely the heir to a vast
fortune!
[SHIZUKO] Three visitors'
passes, please.
[RECEPTIONIST] Yes, ma'am.
[SHIZUKO] I wonder where he went
to...
[SAKURA] Huh? Isn't that him
over there?
[GIRLS] So handsome!
[SAKURA] Ooh, look! Those girls
are practically swarming all
over him!
[SAKURA] What are you looking
at, Misaki?
Pay attention‐ we can't let Usui
out of our sight!
[MISAKI] You, but that doesn't
mean...!
[SAKURA] Huh? He's already gone.
[SHIZUKO] Both of you, hurry!
[SHIZUKO] Usui has already left.
Quickly, let's wait for him
outside.
[BOTH] Uh, okay.
[MISAKI] So now where are we?
[SHIZUKO] A high‐class,
tailor‐made suit store.
[SAKURA] I was right again? Wow,
I'm really good at this!
[SHIZUKO] Just who is Usui,
exactly?
[SAKURA] I already told you!
He's the heir to vast fortune!
[SHIZUKO] Let's proceed.
[MISAKI] Huh? We're going in?
[SHIZUKO] Of course we are.
[SAKURA] These look so
expensive!
[MISAKI] Jeez, this is the
biggest waste of space
I've ever seen. Couldn't they
put out some more product?
[CLERK] Welcome. Is there
something I can help you find?
[SAKURA] Uh oh...
[SHIZUKO] No, good sir.
We are merely looking‐
we will let you know
if we need any help.
[CLERK] Please let me know
if I can be of any assistance.
[SAKURA] Shizuko, that was
awesome!
[MISAKI] You sounded so mature.
[SHIZUKO] Let us continue to
look for Usui.
[MISAKI] Yeah.
[SAKURA] Hey, don't leave me!
[MISAKI] I wonder if they're as
expensive as they look...
[MISAKI] How much is this one
is...?
[MISAKI] Five hundred thousand?!
Is that some kinda joke?!
[SHIZUKO] This section is only
for pre‐made suits.
The custom‐made suits in there
probably cost twice as much.
[MISAKI] I can't believe clothes
this expensive actually exist...
[SAKURA] I don't see Usui
anywhere in the store...
[MISAKI] Oh, I know‐ he probably
wandered in her on accident,
saw how much these suits cost,
and then took off.
[SHIZUKO] No, it is possible
that he was guided toward the
VIP room.
[BOTH] VIP?!
[SHIZUKO] As I thought... the
VIP room.
[BOTH] VIP!
[CLERK] It suits you quite well.
[USUI] I believe it does SUIT me
well, sir.
[CLERK] Understood, sir.
[USUI] Thanks.
[SHIZUKO] He's coming this way.
[MISAKI] The more I find out
about him the more confused I
get...
[SHIZUKO] Let's follow him.
[SAKURA] Yay!
[MISAKI] What's this?
[SHIZUKO] It appears to
be a restaurant.
The name written there says
"Ultra High Class."
[SAKURA] What should I do?
My imagination was right AGAIN!
This is kinda scary!
[MISAKI] Well, since it's a
restaurant,
I guess we can't go in and
follow him anymore, can we?
[SHIZUKO] Let's go.
[SAKURA] Oh, we're going in?
Yay!
[MISAKI] Huh?!
[WAITER] Hello‐ would you happen
to have a reservation with us?
[SHIZUKO] It would seem the
other members of our party are
not yet here.
May we wait for them inside?
[WAITER] Of course.
Please, let me show you
to a table.
[MISAKI] Isn't it bad manners
for me to wear a hat inside?
[SHIZUKO] It's part of your
outfit, so I doubt they will
even notice.
[WAITER] Shall I bring you some
drink menus?
[SHIZUKO] No, water is fine,
good sir.
[WAITER] Very well.
[MISAKI] I think the person
I've learned the most about
today is you Shizuko‐
I don't think this is a
side of you I've ever
seen before.
[SAKURA] When you do something,
you go all out, dontcha?
[SHIZUKO] Now then, let us
observe Usui.
[SAKURA] Is he waiting for
someone?
[SHIZUKO] He very well could.
It's hard to imagine that one
would eat alone in a high‐class
restaurant such as this.
[SAKURA] Maybe we'll finally
get to see what his
family looks like?
Oh! What if he's waiting
for his secret girlfriend?
[SAKURA] I wonder who it's gonna
be?
[SAKURA] What? What is it,
Misaki?
[SAKURA] Wha‐What? Don't tell
me‐ is that who Usui's been
waiting for?
[SAKURA] She's going over
there...
[SAKURA] Ahh! Look, he just
waved at her! So he really WAS
waiting for a girl!
[SAKURA] Or, at least, it just
looks like that.
Even though she's walking
towards his table, there's still
a chance we're wrong.
[SAKURA] We still can't tell for
sure.
[SAKURA] Huh? Look at that...
[SAKURA] For some reason I'm
really relieved...
[SHIZUNO] We were completely
fooled.
[SHIZUKO] What is it, Misaki?
[SHIZUKO] Careful, he'll spot
you.
[MISAKI] Sorry, I'm going home.
[MISAKI] I swear... what the
heck am I even doing here?
[SAKURA] Misaki!
[SAKURA] You're really going?
Yeah. I wasn't interested in
Usui's secrets to begin with.
[SHIZUKO] I see. If that's how
you feel,
[SAKURA] Double glasses!
[SHIZUKO] I see.
If that's how you feel,
then perhaps we should
end this here.
[MISAKI] What the heck?!
How is he even running like
that?!
[SAKURA] When did he put on a
kimono?
[SHIZUKO] It would seem
the game is back on‐
let us resume our
pursuit!
Come on, Misaki!
[MISAKI] Hold on‐!
[USUI] All clear, go right ahead
ma'am.
[SAKURA] Man, I'm beat!
It's gotten so late
I had to take off my sunglasses.
[SHIZUKO] Usui is truly a riddle
wrapped in an enigma.
[SAKURA] Is this the kind of
stuff he does every single day?
[SAKURA] I think I've had enough
for one day. I'm out!
[SHIZUKO] I am as well.
[SAKURA] If you don't mind,
I'll be taking back my super
secret disguise, too!
[SAKURA] See you later, Misaki.
It was actually kinda fun,
wasn't it?
[SHIZUKO] Well then, Misaki,
we'll see you tomorrow.
[SAKURA] Oh! It's faster to cut
through that park over there.
[SHIZUKO] Very well. Let's go.
[MISAKI] I'm so confused...
[MISAKI] Guess I'll head home,
too.
[MISAKI] Usui?
Owow! Hold on a second!
[MISAKI] Look at you getting
beat up by a cat!
[USUI] For whatever reason,
animals really don't like me.
[USUI] They say animals and
babies know if someone is kind
or not‐
guess they know a stalker when
they see one.
[MISAKI] I know you're kind,
Usui.
[MISAKI] You act like you're all
cool and aloof,
but here you are helping a stray
kitten off the street.
[USUI] You sure about that?
Maybe I knew you were
following me
and set this whole thing up to
make myself look good.
[MISAKI] You could've,
but you're not that kind of guy,
right?
Wait a minute!
You knew we were following you
from the start, didn't you?!
So you were just dragging us all
across town for your own
personal enjoyment, is that it?!
[USUI] With those costumes on
it's not exactly like you'd
blend in, right?
[MISAKI] Don't give me that!
I thought the exact same thing!
[USUI] Still... it was nice
that you showed
an interest
in me for a change.
Guess there's a first time for
everything.
[MISAKI] Wh‐what are you saying?
It's not like I was there
because I wanted to be...
[USUI] If you just ask, I'll
show you everything there is to
know about me.
[USUI] Here. My address is‐
[MISAKI] No thanks.
[USUI] Huh?
[MISAKI] No matter how hard
I try I can't figure you out,
and I never have any idea what
you're thinking.
[MISAKI] So, yeah, maybe I did
feel like
trying to learn a little bit
more about you.
[MISAKI] And as a result,
I learned everything about you
that I really needed to know...
[MISAKI] that I could care less
about your private life!
In fact, the less I know the
better!
So you're saying that regardless
of my past or my background,
that no matter what you love me
for ME, right?
[MISAKI] Are you an idiot?!
How could you possibly have
come to that conclusion?!
[MISAKI] Just hurry up and go
home!
[USUI] Yeah, yeah.
[MISAKI] And don't
make any stops‐
just go straight home.
[USUI] Oh, you can come back
to my house if you'd like,
Miss President.
[MISAKI] No thank you!
[USUI] Shoot.
[MINAKO] This is Minako Ayuzawa.
Thank you for always looking
after Misaki.
[SUZUNA] So this is where you
are, Mom.
[MINAKO] Oh, Suzuna. I forgot to
give Usui a present.
What do you think of this?
[SUZUNA] One of the dolls
you paint faces on?
It's the perfect present!
[MISAKI] Huh. I wonder if he'd
like this...
[USUI] Ooh, that's a nice doll.
[MISAKI] Make it a matching set
with this bowl made out
of scrap wood.
[USUI] Ooh, that's a nice bowl.
[MISAKI] Next up is the sports
festival, huh?
[SAKURA] No! Please don't make
me kiss anyone!
[MISAKI] It's all right.
I'll protect you, Sakura.