[MISAKI'S GHOST] Continuing from
where we left off last time,
everyone's at the Yumesaki
Cultural Festival...
[USUI]
This place is ridiculously
crowded. Let's go somewhere
else.
[MISAKI]
E‐easier said than done.
I came to this festival because
I was worried about Sakura,
so it makes no sense that we'd
get separated, but it would make
even less sense to go home.
[YUKIMURA]
Maybe there are other students
from our school here, too.
[KANOU] Maybe.
[MISAKI] It can't be helped.
I just have to kill time with
Usui until the show finishes.
[ICHIROU]
That grilled squid was great!
[JIROU] It WAS really great.
[SABUROU] What do we eat next?
[SHIROU GOROU] Chicken nuggets!
[ICHIROU JIROU] Okay, let's go!
[MISAKI] (sigh) There're way
too many people here!
[USUI] Yeah. Chomp chomp.
[MISAKI] SHOCK!
[MISAKI]
How did you get all
that stuff so fast?!
[USUI] For some reason people
just started giving me things.
[USUI] They were like,
"Here, try this."
[MISAKI] "For some reason"?!
There's gotta be another reason!
[USUI]
Well, maybe it's because... I
made the flowers bloom again!
[MISAKI] Uh...
[USUI] Oh, jeez. Not again.
Let's get out of here.
[MISAKI] Wahhhh!
(Girls gushing over Usui)
[GIRL]
Huh? Where'd the hottie go?
[MISAKI] I don't understand...
but don't make anymore flowers
bloom okay?
Is that some kind
of magic trick?
Huh? I don't really think
it's a magic trick, more
of an illusion.
Whatever it is,
what are they for?!
Huh? A sense of rivalry?
[MISAKI] Rivalry with what?!
Come on, stop being so angry.
Why don't you eat something‐
it'll make you feel better.
(breath) Thanks but no thanks,
I don't need any‐
[USUI] Here.
It's pretty tasty.
Well? How is it?
(mumbling) It's good.
[MISAKI, thinking] This is
weird. It's just like‐‐
[USUI] You were thinking it's
like a date. Right?
[MISAKI] Uh?
[USUI] That looks good on you.
You were reading my mind
again, weren't you?
You perverted alien!
What's with those superhuman
abilities of yours?!
Of making flowers bloom,
reading people's minds...
Just who or WHAT, are you, huh?!
(laughing)
Wha? Why are
you laughing?!
[USUI] Sorry. But you...
[MISAKI] Huh?
You were thinking the exact
same thing that I was.
[USUI] Where are you going?
[MISAKI] Uh‐ SOMEWHERE.
It's a festival, so I can't
just keep sitting around.
[USUI] I see.
[ICHIROU] We ate almost
everything, huh?
[JIROU] We sure did.
[SABUROU] Now to check out the
events.
[SHIROU]
What's this "Haunted Mansion"?
[JIROU]
Let's go see how
haunted it really is!
[ICHIROU] Let's go!
Suzuna, did you ever win that
game you were going for?
Yep, I won with a
single postcard.
That's awesome!
I wonder if they have a
sweepstakes club here.
[FRIEND B] I highly doubt it.
[FRIEND A] Let's find some
more food.
[YUKIMURA]
Kanou, should we have
some chicken nuggets?
[KANOU]
That sounds good to me.
[YOUNG SIS] Froggie...
[BIG SIS] Yeah, a big froggie.
[MISAKI]
Dammit! My face is
STILL burning.
[GIRL A]
We have the perfect
event for you two.
It's called the Love Trial!
The bounds of your love will be
put to the ultimate test!
Y‐you've got it all wrong, we're
not like that‐
[GIRL]
The rules are simple!
The two of you follow
a set course,
and at each check point one of
you will take on a challenge!
[BOY]
If you can't clear one of the
stages, then you're out!
But if you clear ALL stages and
finish the game...
you'll be treated to
an ultra‐special event
after the festival.
[GIRL] However!
[STUDENTS] Amazing! Whoa!
[GIRL] You can't let go of
each other's hands till you
reach the goal.
Now then, what kind of trials
can you two overcome to stay
together?!
Are you up for the challenge?
[USUI] We'll do it.
What?!
Are you serious?!
If we want to be together...
we have to "attempt the
great challenge that
awaits," remember?
[USUI] Let's give it a try.
[ERIKA]
You are fire and water, with
the worst of compatibility.
Don't tell me you're
still worried about
that fortune‐telling?
I just want to try taking
on a big challenge
together, that's all.
[STUDENTS]
Thank you for accepting
and good luck!
[MISAKI]
I swear. How can you waste money
on something like this?
For the price on one coin we
have the wealth of an experience
that will last a life time.
Whatever you say...
If you think about it,
we're getting a good deal.
[USUI] Oh, that's right.
Take your ribbon off.
This is our proof of
participation. Make
sure it's visible.
[MISAKI]
Why do I have to put it on?
[USUI] Because it will look
best on you.
[MISAKI] Uuuh.
[USUI]
Apparently, you get to
keep this when we're done.
See? It isn't a total
waste after all.
Besides, it's good to have
fun once in a while, isn't it?
Also...
If you keep scowling like that,
you'll get wrinkles.
Well, let's get going!
[MISAKI]
Stupid Usui!
You're such a‐
[USUI] I know.
You absolutely... hate me...
isn't that right?
[MISAKI] Uh...
[MISAKI]
Don't say things like
that... stupid Usui.
[SHIZUKO]
I am leaving now.
[SAKURA, whining]
Shizuko!
[MC]
Up next is a short skit
by the famous second‐year duo,
Kamiyama and Ohno!
[KAMIYAMA] I'm Kamiyama!
[OHNO] I'm Ohno.
[BOTH]
Together, we're the Rarr!
Go‐Go‐Go, Run Ma‐Ma‐Ma‐Ma
Aaaargh! Badda‐bing, badda‐‐
This skit is
TERRIBLE, Sakura!
Hey, that's not my fault!
Just how much longer
till Yumemishi comes out?
Um, about two more hours?
[SHIZUKO] Good. Then that means
I have 2 hours to lecture you.
[SAKURA] Shizuko!
Why do we have to wait so long
to see a ridiculous concert?
[SHIZUKO] Ugh. At this rate, I
think it's probably for the best
that we got separated from
Misaki and Usui when we did.
I'm sorry...
[MISAKI, thinking]
Why did things have
to turn out like this?
Why? Why do I have to hold
his hand for this game? Unhh...
[USUI] It's like a date, right?
(Heart beat)
[MISAKI] Uh! No!
I came here with Sakura and
Shizuko,
so why did this have to
happen‐?! Uunnnhhh!
[GIRL]
Okay, are you two ready to go?!
[BOY]
Love Trial... Start now!
What's the matter? We only have
10 minutes to do this, remember?
[USUI]
Try not to hold me back too
much, Miss President.
[MISAKI]
Who's holding who back?!
I'm so sick of this
competitive attitude of
yours I could scream!
Hrm? This may not be our
school, but it's not good to
run in the halls, you know.
[Misaki] Shut up! It's a race!
[USUI] THIS is how you run a
race.
[MISAKI]
The floor's too smooth.
This feels weird!
[YUKIMURA]
We haven't seen that many people
we know, have we, Kanou?
[KANOU] Indeed.
[GIRL] Hrm. What's that
strange sound? Aahah!
[MISAKI] Here's our proof of
participation!
Aah, I can't believe
that took 3 minutes.
It would have only taken
a minute if I had done it
by myself.
Oh yeah! Well if I'd been by
myself, it only would've taken
me 30 seconds!
[USUI] We're ready to hear the
rules of the game.
[MISAKI] Raharhaharahra!
[GIRL] Here you go! Please eat
this in 10 minutes or less!
[MISAKI] Jeez, between the two
of us, this will be no problem‐
[FEMALE 26D] However, only one
person can eat it. Hm.
[USUI]
I'm sensing a bit of hostility.
All the boys manage to clear it
just in the nick of time.
Do your best for
your girlfriend.
[MISAKI] Let's do
rock‐paper‐scissors.
What, you're not gonna say
something like "Oh, I can't
eat this" and make me do it?
What? Why the heck would I?
[MISAKI] One, two, three.
Fine by me, I won't let a single
drop of that soup go to waste!
Huh?
Excuse me, but is it okay
if I change hands...?
[GIRL]
You'll be disqualified!
Eh... Fine, I'll
just use my left hand then‐
[USUI]
Then I guess my role...
is to do THIS.
I'll feed you, so make sure
you savor every last bite.
[MISAKI]
Th‐That's not necessary!
I can eat it myself! Give
me those chopsticks!
[USUI]
I think we're ready to begin.
[GIRL]
Let's go! One, two...
[GIRLS]
Chinese noodles! Fat noodles!
You're all salty noodles!
[GIRL] Let the game begin!
[USUI] Here. Say "Aah."
[USUI]
If you don't hurry, you won't be
able to eat it in 10 minutes.
[BOY] For once the
girl is trying it!
[GIRL] Good luck to you!
[USUI] You want me to blow on
it first?
N‐No! I can eat it as‐is!
[MISAKI, thinking]
Calm down‐ getting embarrassed
would be just what Usui wants!
[USUI] Huh? President, you're
BAD at this.
Look, look! It's right here.
See? Looksie, looksie!
It's over here! Right here!
C'mon now, President!
[BOY A]
Hey, I hear something
awesome's goin' on.
[BOY B]
Class 3‐1's ramen shop?
Oh, you mean that special
competition right?
[BOY A]
Yeah. Apparently, one couple
is eating with full‐on,
superhuman strength!
[BOY C]
Next up is Class 3‐2's
card game, right?
That second‐ year Ikumi is
second‐to‐none at Speed,
but that devil girl defeated
him in no time flat!
[IKUMI]
Yeah, it was the devil I tell
you! She really was the devil!
[BOY A]
The next thing was
even more awesome!
[BOY B]
Class 3‐3's ping pong, right?
[BOY D] Normally, if you
can't use your good hand,
you'd be on the defensive...
[MISAKI] Hyaaa!
[BOTH] What?!
[BOY A] Wait, so that girl's
NOT left‐handed?
I'm glad we won, but for
some reason I couldn't get
up to my usual strength...
[USUI]
The "'Cuz I'm right‐handed"
excuse, is it?
[MISAKI]
No! I just don't feel well!
[USUI] Huh.
[BOY C] That... That's no
normal couple. They're like...
[ALL]
Some sort of "super" couple!
[BOY]
Welcome to the Balloon Quiz!
First, you must find the
balloon marked "Winner."
When you find it, pop it open,
take out the question inside and
answer it as quickly as
possible.
You have five minutes.
And... Start!
[MISAKI] I have the feeling
we're being made into some kind
of spectacle.
[USUI] Maybe we're
standing out too much.
[USUI]
I wonder if the distraction
is necessary anymore...
Huh? Did you say something?
[USUI] Not really.
[MISAKI] Smoosh!
It's a race, to see which of us
can find the winning balloon.
Interesting.
I accept your challenge!
[MISAKI] Uuhh... Whoa!
Uh, Usui, look, I already‐!
Found... it..,
Wh‐what're you just standing
there for? We have a time limit,
so hurry up and‐
Oh, that's right.
Eh?
We have to...
hurry up and pop it.
[SHIZUKO]
Now listen here, Sakura: I have
had just about enough of this!
He dresses all glitzy, in a
fashion that makes no sense, and
yet he has the audacity to act
so pretentious!
I have absolutely no
idea what you see in him!
The more time we spend in this
human mob the angrier I get!
[SAKURA] Shizuko...
[SHIZUKO, muttering]
Ah, I'm sorry, Sakura, I said
too much please forgive me.
[SAKURA, thinking]
Shizuko's starting to lose it!
I just need a moment to calm
down and I'll be just fine.
[SAKURA]
I'm really sorry. Shizuko...
Even if you ask me what I see
in him it's hard to explain...
I mean‐ Yeah, I think he's
the coolest guy I've ever met,
and I respect him for following
his dreams no matter what, so
there's that but...
[SAKURA] But... it's so much
more than that. It's something
that words can't describe.
[SAKURA]
When you love someone... you
just can't help how you feel.
[SAKURA]
So if someone objects, or even
if you know it's not right,
once you've felt that feeling...
you just can't stop.
[BOY]
You've successfully completed
the Love Trial! Congratulations!
[GIRL] That ticket can be
used for a special event at
the festival's after‐party.
Please, make sure to enjoy
tonight to the fullest!
[MISAKI'S GHOST] How nice.
Huh? How come Misa
isn't working today?
I don't know.
Don't ask me.
Did she have to run an
errand or something?
She should've asked ME
to come along, too.
Why would she do
something like that,
you perverted idiot?
Oh my. You're all looking very
relaxed today, Masters.
[SHIROKAWA]
We're putty in your hands.
[KUROSAKI]
It's like, we don't
know who's who anymore.
[SARASHINA]
In fact, it's almost like
we're not even human.
It makes me so happy to see you
relax yourselves so fully here
at Maid Latte. Please make
yourselves at home.
[ALL] Okay.
[HONOKA]
I'm sorry for the wait.
Here is your cream
soda, Masters.
[ALL] Wow!
[ALL] That's it. There it
is, there it is...!
[SUBARU]
Manager, I'm so sorry I'm late!
[ERIKA]
And I had to stay late to do an
assignment. I'm sorry, Manager.
[SATSUKI]
No worries! I'm just glad
the two of you are here.
[KUROSAKI]
Hey, how do we drink this?
[SARASHINA]
We have to go back to our
original forms to do that.
[SHIROKAWA]
How do we do that again?
[ALL] Uh...
(Students welcoming)
Well, that was a lot of fun.
You were having more
fun taunting me
than you were playing
those stupid games!
So you're saying you didn't
have any fun at all?
Uh, I... Well, I wouldn't say I
had "fun", but...
Shouldn't you go get your bag?
Oh... yeah...
(Concert starting,
crowd cheering)
(Sakura excited giggles)
(Happy chuckles)
[BOY] It's already started!
[MISAKI] Sounds like the
concert's finally started.
[USUI] It looks like they're
a lot later than planned.
What makes you say that, Usui?
[USUI] It's written right here.
[CROWD] Hana o!
[CROWD] Zutto!
[CROWD] Hana wa!
[MISAKI]
Geez, the closer we get to the
stage, the more crowded it gets.
That's why I said we should meet
up with them AFTER the show.
I thought it would be better
if we were close by when it
finished! GAH!
[MISAKI] Ah! Usui!
[USUI]
You okay? Afraid
you'll get lost?
[USUI]
If you want...
I can hold your hand.
[MISAKI, angrily]
Argh! That won't be necessary!
(Giddy chuckles)
[SHIZUKO] Sakura! You must get
a hold of yourself! Your
behavior is incomprehensible!
[MISAKI] Hello, Sakura?
Looks like the show's over, huh?
What? You can't meet up?
C‐C‐Cuz Kuuga...
K‐Kuuga... Uh, um‐
[SHIZUKO]
Jeez, just let ME explain!
It seems that a certain
someone from Yumemishi
will be joining us to take
a walk around the festival.
Huh?! Someone from Yumemishi?
Yeesh. What the heck.
For a minute, I thought I was
going to get tailed again.
Uh...
[SHIZUKO] Mr. Kuuga called
earlier to say he wished
to walk around the festival,
and wanted us to tag along as
"camouflage."
Okay, I understand.
I'll call you guys back
a little later.
[KUUGA]
What? You don't glare
at me like that.
Don't worry, I'm not
interested in you.
[KUUGA]
I've had my fill of that
scary face of yours.
[MISAKI]
What are you after?
[KUUGA]
You mean Sakura?
Am I not allowed to walk
around the festival with her?
If you ask, she won't refuse.
Are you using her because
she's convenient?
As always, you're
one scary lady.
To be honest, I don't trust you
as far as I can throw you.
But Sakura was trying her
hardest to convince me that
you'd changed, so I came here
to see for myself.
I've changed, huh?
[MISAKI] Staaaare
[KUUGA]
What're you giving
me that look for?
[MISAKI]
Please excuse my "scary" face.
Since I have no idea
how you've "changed,"
I have to keep staring until
I see it for myself.
[KUUGA] You just wouldn't
understand.
[SAKURA]
Kuuga! I'm here to
visit you again!
She's the only girl who's
ever tried to really see
me for what I really am.
Uh? So does that mean
you're actually in l‐‐
[KUUGA] Stop!
You are WAY too overprotective.
Just go off and be with your
boyfriend, and leave me in
peace, will ya? GAH!
[MISAKI]
Boyfriend?
That waiter guy who
called himself a
stalker or whatever.
N‐No, you've got it wrong!
He's just a perverted weirdo
stalker‐ nothing more!
Huh, don't tell me, are you
seriously still making that
guy hold himself back?
What are you...?
Geez, not only are
you a mood‐killer,
but you're a violent stick in
the mud‐
I couldn't spend a day with you
even if someone paid me!
That's MY line you
stupid son of a‐!
Aah, how scary.
See ya. Medusa.
[MISAKI, thinking]
What did he mean... he's
"holding himself back"? Uh?
[USUI]
Sorry for the wait. It was
crowded so it took longer
than I thought.
What're you‐
Is something wrong?
No... It's nothing really.
[MISAKI]
Well, at the end of the day,
least I did what I set out to
do, I think.
[USUI]
Huh? That's a pretty
anticlimactic ending.
[MISAKI]
It's not like there's really
anything else I can do anyway.
[USUI]
Well, if everything's all
wrapped up here... should
we head out?
N‐No. While we're here,
I... I'd like to stay for
the after‐party. You know?
[MISAKI] Usui, are...
Are you okay on time?
Uhhh... That was an
incredibly unexpected line.
[MISAKI] Blgh!
The heck?! I was
just asking, okay!
Is that so bad?!
If you don't want to,
I'll go on my own!
[USUI] I'll go.
After all, we still have that
special ticket we won in
that love challenge.
[MISAKI] Oh yeah...
[MISAKI]
So THIS is what they meant when
they said "special event"?
[GIRL A]
And the size is just right.
It's perfect!
[GIRL B]
A special dress to make a
special memory on a special day!
[GIRL A]
Have as much fun as you
like with it, okay?
[GIRL B]
Now then‐ your Romeo awaits!
Hey.
That looks good on you, Juliet.
Don't call me that,
it's embarrassing,
[USUI] Apparently, they'll be
doing fireworks
at the after‐party, too.
[MISAKI] Is that so?
[USUI] I'd like to find
somewhere to watch them.
[MISAKI] Okay...
[USUI] Oh, perfect. We'll be
able to see the fireworks, and
no one will bother us.
Are we allowed in here?
We're not doing anything wrong,
so it should be fine.
[BOY A] Are you ready?
[BOY B] Hang on!
[USUI] What's wrong?
Uh....
Ayuzawa...
What's with YOU?!
There's nothing wrong at all.
Is that right? Then I'm glad.
Maybe we should
go somewhere else.
It would be more fun to see
the bonfire up close, right?
A‐Are you holding back?
About the fireworks?
I don't care too much about‐
That's not what I'm
talking about! Are you...
Have you been holding
yourself back all this
time because of me?
Why do you think that?
[MISAKI]
N‐no reason, I just, sort of,
thought maybe that was the case.
[USUI]
Huh. How perceptive of you.
So you HAVE been holding
back? What have‐?
[USUI] How cruel, Ayuzawa.
Are you... trying to
make me say it?
[USUI]
Then, if you answer my question,
I'll answers yours, too.
[MISAKI] What...?
[USUI]
What makes you care about me?
What kind of question is
that... I guess my answer
is, I don't know.
You don't know... huh?
Then, did you know...
that at times like this, it's
impossible for you to lie?
[MISAKI] Wh‐What are you
talking about?
Ayuzawa, why is your
face turning so red?
It's not red at all‐
[USUI] Are you nervous?
[MISAKI] N‐no, I'm not!
[USUI] Ayuzawa, aren't YOU the
one who's holding back?
[USUI]
I'm sorry. I went too far.
[MISAKI]
I am holding back...
[USUI] Uh?!
[MISAKI]
I've BEEN holding back.
Why did it turn out this way?!
Why did it have to be you...?
I don't get it at all! You're
a pervert, and all you do is
piss me off...
[MISAKI] You're still running
ahead of me, making it look so
easy.
[USUI] Ayuzawa?
You make fun of me all the time!
[USUI] Calm down! What are
you...?
[MISAKI] This is your fault. If
we hadn't done that stupid game,
I wouldn't have realized.
The truth is‐ I've always
wanted to hold your hand!
Just when I think I've got
you figured out, it's like
you lose me again.
What are you thinking?
I just don't get it...
I don't understand why my heart
won't stop racing when I'm
around you?
Or why do I have to get
so lonely when we're apart?
I‐ Why are you... the only one
who can make me feel like this?
[MISAKI] Stupid Usui.
Why do you always have
to pick a fight with me?
[USUI] You really...
are cruel, Ayuzawa.
How much longer do you
plan to make me hold back?
I pick fights with you because
I want to see your reactions.
Normally, you're the
hardheaded student council
president,
but suddenly you'll look
cute, or surprised,
or you'll be completely
worked up over nothing.
[USUI] You asked me if
I've been holding back?
I've held back so many times
that I can't give an answer.
[MISAKI] Huh?
[USUI] Just like right now.
[USUI]
Do you want to know what
I'm thinking, right this
very second, Misa?
I love you, Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI] I really...
I really hate you.
[USUI] True to form...
You're too cruel, Ayuzawa.
[MISAKI] Stupid Usui...
[MISAKI] Ah! I forgot I need
an apron for today's lesson!
I'm so screwed!
Don't worry, Sis,
I've got you covered.
We happen to have an
apron I won in the sweepstakes.
I'm sure wearing this
would make them happy.
Make WHO happy?!
Oh, who indeed...
(laughing)
Aah, it's so nice to enjoy
some peace and quiet
before the shop opens...
[AOI] Satsuki! I got
kicked out again!
[AOI] I'll be counting
on you, okay?
[SATSUKI] Oh, okay...
[SHINTANI] I know now, I gotta
make myself into a better man!
After all, I'm going
up against that guy!
[USUI] It's not "That guy."
The name's Usui.
[SHINTANI]
And I'm definitely
gonna beat him!
[SHINTANI] G'morning, Misaki!
Why are you coming to school
eating bread crusts?!
[USUI] Misa, I love you.
[SAKURA] Oh! Misaki!
[SHIZUKO] Misaki.
[YUKIMURA] Miss President!
[KANOU] Impossible.
[TORA] Interesting, huh, Maki?
[MAKI] It is.
[TRIO] Misa's the best!