(MISAKI sighs)
[YUKIMURA]
Thanks for your help, Kanou.
I owe you one!
[KANOU] Not at all.
[MISAKI] Kanou?
[YUKIMURA]
He was nice enough to help me
carry these papers.
[MISAKI]
When did you two get so close?
[KANOU]
I thought that if I
spent a little more
time with Yukimura,
it would help me get over
my weakness with women.
[YUKIMURA] Huuhhh... I already
told you‐ I'm NOT a girl!
[MISAKI] Uh...
[KANOU] Indeed.
[YUKIMURA]
Now you're just agreeing without
meaning it again!
[KANOU] Indeed.
[MISAKI] YUKIMURA.
Y‐yes, ma'am?
[MISAKI & HAGIMOTO]
Get stronger...
[YUKIMURA]
Ah! For some reason, I can hear
what you're all thinking!
[YUKIMURA]
I'll show you! Take a good look!
Cuz the next time you see me,
I'll be the manliest man you've
ever seen!
[YUKIMURA]
I'm gonna become‐
a man among men!
[YUKIMURA]
All right, I'm going to go get
the rest of the papers. By
myself! ...So there!
[KANOU]
Let me help you with that!
[YUKIMURA]
Forget it! I'm doing it alone!
[KANOU]
It's impossible for
one person to do.
[YUKIMURA]
But when I do, I'll be so manly
that you'll be shocked!
[YUKIMURA]
Then I'll pay you
back for your help!
[MISAKI, thinking]
Eh‐heh. We've found a good
guardian. Heh.
[MISAKI, thinking]
Oh, yeah. Speaking of "payback."
[USUI] You want to pay me back?
[MISAKI]
(heavy breaths) Yes.
You helped me with that stalker,
the sports festival, and KANOU,
among other things.
I can't keep staying
in your debt like this.
[USUI]
Then how about you be my
personal maid for just one day.
[MISAKI]
Ah?! There's no other way?
[USUI]
Uh, well... Let's see...
Is that really what you want to
do‐ to make me your "personal
maid" for a day?
[MISAKI]
I already knew you were a
pervert, but I didn't think
you were on this level.
[MISAKI'S GHOST]
He's the real deal.
If that's the best thing
you can come up with,
that actually makes me
kind of worried.
[USUI]
Oh really? So you're saying
you'd rather do something more
promiscuous?
[MISAKI]
Whaaat?!
[USUI]
I was just joking.
[MISAKI]
Ugh...
[USUI]
Time for work, Miss President.
(MISAKI growling)
[MISAKI]
Just what are you planning,
Usui you idiot?!
[SHIROKAWA]
"Grave misfortune. You may lose
something important to you.
Watch out, Master."
[SHIROKAWA] (cry of agony)
This is terrible! What's this
"something important"?!
[SHIROKAWA] (panicking)
Is it that? Or is it THAT?
What is it?!
[MISAKI]
Shut up...
[SATSUKI]
That was the only bad fortune
we put in the whole lot.
[SUBARU]
So in a way he's actually
lucky at being unlucky.
[SARASHINA] Calm down, Shiroyan.
[KUROSAKI] Yeah, don't worry‐
WE got great fortunes!
[SHIROKAWA]
Whaddya mean "don't worry"?!
That doesn't help me at all!
[MISAKI]
Please be quiet, Master! They're
only handmade fortune cookies.
[KUROSAKI]
Uh? Then, Misa, you have one!
[SARASHINA]
If you get the same fortune as
Shiroyan, it should cheer him up
a bit.
[SHIROKAWA]
UH?
[MISAKI]
Small Fortune...
[KUROSAKI & SARASHINA]
That sucks...
[SHIROKAWA] (life draining)
[MISAKI]
"Let's repay those debts..."
[SUBARU]
I'm sorry, Master, but
we're already closed for
the night‐ Uh?
[MAKI]
Pardon our intrusion.
But we are not customers.
[MISAKI]
The vice president
of Miyabigaoka?
[MAKI]
Excuse me, but where might I
find the owner of this shop?
[SUBARU] Um, well...
[SATSUKI] I'm the store
owner. And you are...?
[MAKI] My apologies
for the suddenness.
[SATSUKI] Uh?
[MAKI]
But I am interested in
purchasing this café from you.
[ALL]
Huh!?
Allow me to introduce
myself. I am Kanade Maki.
[MAKI]
I represent the
Maki Dining Group.
[SATSUKI]
Huh? The Maki Dining Group?
[AOI] Are they famous?
[SUBARU] Aoi, you haven't
heard of them?
[SATSUKI] The Maki Dining Group
is a major restaurant company
that runs everything from
casual dining restaurants
to ultra‐exclusive bistros.
To think that you know so
much about my father's company.
It is truly an honor.
[AOI]
He's the boss's son?
[MAKI]
Actually, in the near future,
we will be opening a new
restaurant.
[MAKI]
When considering the clientele,
we found this location to be
ideal,
so we entered into negotiations.
[SATSUKI] Um, with whom?
[MAKI] The building owner.
[TRIO]
The building owner?!
[SUBARU]
You're going to buy
the entire building?
[MAKI]
Unfortunately, we could not come
to an agreement...
[OWNER]
Hmph! I'm keepin' this building
till the day I die!
[OWNER]
I ain't gonna go botherin' my
tenants with this hullabaloo!
[OWNER] Get the heck outta here,
you whippersnapper! I ain't
goin' nowhere!
[MAKI] Therefore, I've been
[SARASHINA] There's no way we're
gonna let that happen!
[SHIROKAWA]
You're sayin' Maid Latte would
have to shut down, right?!
[KUROSAKI]
Go open your fancy‐shmancy
restaurant somewhere else!
[MAKI] The kind of shop we would
like to open here is...
[TRIO] Listen to us!
[MAKI]
Well, as employees of this shop,
I'm sure you require little
explanation. It's a butler café.
[SARASHINA] I object!
[KUROSAKI] That's not
cute at all!
[SHIROKAWA] Long live maids!
[MAKI] And so, we would like to
open our shop here if possible.
[TRIO] We said, listen to us!
[MISAKI]
Isn't it a little much to
buy an entire building for
one little café?
[MAKI] Indeed. That's why we
plan to demolish the building
and construct an English‐style
manor in its place.
[SATSUKI]
Uh...
I suppose you could say
it's less a café and more
of a restaurant.
[MAKI]
We also plan on offering a
full‐course dinner menu.
[MAKI]
Essentially, it will be the
ultimate butler café experience.
[AOI]
Wait a minute! So your so‐called
"butlers" are just glorified
waiters?
You can't just call it
a "butler café" and‐!
[TORA]
Of that he is well
aware. Trust me.
[MISAKI]
(shocked)
After all, he is the
incredibly talented vice
president of Miyabigaoka
High School, you know.
[MISAKI, thinking]
Miyabigaoka's student council
president: Tora Igarashi!
[MISAKI]
What the hell is he plotting?
He performs his support
functions as vice president
most excellently.
[TORA]
You could say he knows firsthand
the fulfillment that comes from
supporting one's master.
[TORA]
I have no doubt he will be
able to create a truly
splendid restaurant.
[TORA]
He has my support not only as
student council president, but
as his friend as well.
[TORA]
However, if you still doubt the
quality level of his butlers,
why not come to the footman
auditions we'll be holding next
week and see for yourself?
[MISAKI] "Footman"?
[MAKI] Staff members who
work under the supervision
of the butlers.
To hire footmen of the highest
caliber... We will be conducting
our interviews more in the style
of a cattle call audition.
[KUROSAKI]
Auditions?! What is this some
kind of singing competition?!
[SARASHINA] Why're you already
trying to hire people?!
[SHIROKAWA]
No one's said they're gonna sell
this place to you, have they‐?!
[TORA] (menacing)
[TRIO] (frightened)
[TORA] Perhaps we should take
our leave now, Maki.
[MAKI] Sir.
[TORA] They will obviously need
some time to thoroughly think
things over.
[MAKI] Sir.
Although we may be excusing
ourselves for the day, we will
be continuing with our plans to
purchase this building.
[MAKI] Please look over our
offer in detail while
considering this matter‐
[MAKI] I'm sure you will
find the sum agreeable.
[SATSUKI] (dead on the inside)
[MAKI]
However, if you have any
concerns regarding monetary
assistance for outplacement
and store relocation we shall
gladly re‐examine our numbers.
[TORA]
Farewell for now.
[MISAKI]
Please wait!
[MAKI]
May we assist you?
Do you think it wise to be
walking around in public in
attire such as that?
[MISAKI] Why HERE? Are you
doing this because of me?
[BOTH] Hm?
[TORA] Heh..
[MAKI]
What are you‐
[TORA]
Maki. You go ahead.
[MAKI]
Huh? But sir, I‐
[TORA] Maki. That is an order.
[MAKI] Hm?
[MAKI]
Sir.
[MISAKI]
I see your acting is as
good as always, Igarashi.
[TORA] And you...
Have got some interestin'
clothes on, as always.
[MISAKI] Nngh!
[MISAKI] (surprised) Ah?
[TORA]
Y'know, this is the first time
Maki's been trusted to open up
a place all on his own.
[TORA]
I'm just watchin' from
the sidelines.
[TORA]
He's mighty serious about
makin' his shop a success.
[MISAKI]
We're just as serious!
This shop was built through the
hard work of our manager and all
of the Maid Latte employees!
[MISAKI]
And we have loyal customers who
come here every single day!
[MISAKI]
So... Have you thought
about them at all?
[TORA]
You sure do love bein'
a maid, don't you?
[TORA]
You plannin' on becomin' a real
pro and workin' here after you
graduate?
Then you're gonna have to try
takin' on Maki for real.
If you really wanna beat him and
save your maid shop, you gotta
prove just how serious you are.
For example, there's
next week's auditions.
That'd be the perfect
opportunity... to show off your
pro customer service abilities.
[TORA]
Oh, my bad. Girls aren't allowed
to compete. (driving off)
[MISAKI]
I almost forgot. I still owe him
BIG TIME for our last little run
in at Miyabigaoka!
[USUI] That's for sure.
[MISAKI]
I won't forgive him for this!
I WILL get him back,
no matter what it takes!
[SUBARU]
Please allow me to
take your luggage.
[MISAKI]
May I take your hand...?
[BOTH]
My Lady.
[SATSUKI] They're perfect.
(TRIO giggling excitedly)
[SATSUKI]
Misa, Subaru, your
disguises are amazing!
[SATSUKI] There's no way anyone
would guess you're girls!
[SUBARU] Still, it's strange.
To think that taping our chests
down and wearing wigs
would affect our appearance
so profoundly.
[MISAKI] Sorry, Subaru.
[SUBARU] Huh?
About having to drag you
along with me like this...
[SUBARU]
Don't worry. After all,
the participants have to
compete in pairs.
Besides, when I saw how
determined you were to fight
to save Maid Latte...
[SUBARU]
I knew there was no way I could
let you take this on alone!
Right. If we can use these
auditions to show them just how
capable our staff is,
I think we can show them that
we're not going down so easily.
[ERIKA]
Actually, I really wanted to
compete, too, but I have a chest
that can't be hidden! Hehe!
[SUBARU] Yes we're so lucky to
be flat‐chested, aren't we?
[MISAKI] (awkward) Heh...
[MISAKI, thinking]
If it weren't for the fact
that I worked at Maid Latte,
I'm sure those guys never
would've gone after the
store like this.
[MISAKI, thinking]
Because of me, a place that
everyone holds dear, could be
destroyed!
[MISAKI]
I definitely won't
let that happen!
[SATSUKI]
All these guys are
here to try out?
[MISAKI]
There's so many people
I can barely move!
[ERIKA]
It's like dude central
station up in here!
[HONOKA]
I think that guy's afro is
taking up more room than all
these guys combined.
[SATSUKI]
They must've posted
fliers up all over town.
[BUTLER A] Looks like they're
going to test you on your
physical skills more than
anything else, huh?
[BUTLER B]
Yeah, since there's no
interview this thing's
gonna be a walk in the park.
[BUTLER C]
And the pay is just too
good to pass up!
[SUBARU]
"Those interested, please come
to the conference hall," huh?
That's the Maki Dining
Group for you.
They can pull a crowd like
this with the strength of
their name alone.
[MISAKI] Is there something
wrong, Manager?
[SATSUKI]
Um, not really.
I was just thinking about how
we're going up against people
from a different world...
[ALL] (flabbergasted)
[MAKI] My apologies
for the wait.
[MAKI]
Thank you very much
for being here today.
[MAKI]
Without further ado, the
auditions will now begin.
[MISAKI, thinking]
That voice... It's Miyabigaoka's
vice president, Kanade Maki!
[MAKI]
Our first event of
the day will be...
...the marathon.
[HONOKA] Huh? A marathon?
[SUBARU] What kind of audition
is that?
[MAKI] The course will be the
hill you all no doubt traversed
to get here.
[SATSUKI] That sounds hard.
[MAKI]
You will head to the bottom of
the hill, where a turnaround
point has been prepared.
[MAKI] Once you've made your way
back up, you will then head to
the gymnasium, where I, your
judge, will await you.
[SUBARU]
Um... I'm suddenly not
feeling very confident.
[MISAKI]
Don't worry, we'll do our best
to get through this together.
[MAKI]
However, as you will recall
this is an audition of pairs.
[MISAKI] Huh? Gah...
[MAKI] In order to win, you
must piggyback your partner
to the goal line.
[BUTLER D] So it's like a test
of determination?
[MAKI] Although one of you must
carry the other,
[BUTLER E] Looks like
things are heating up.
[MAKI] you are permitted to
change places freely throughout
[BUTLER F] This is a bad joke.
[BUTLER G] Let's just quit now.
[MAKI] The first 50 teams to
cross the finish line will win.
[MAKI] Now then, please assemble
at the starting line.
[MISAKI]
All right‐ let's go, Subaru.
[SUBARU]
Huh? Ah! Uh, are you
sure about this?
Of course‐ this is gonna be a
piece of cake. I'll carry you
the whole way if I have to.
[SATSUKI] Wait, Misa.
[MISAKI] Oh?
[SATSUKI]
That's enough. I've seen what
we're up against.
Winning something... like
this... is just impossible.
I should've known we wouldn't
stand a chance going up against
a wealthy company like this...
Besides, if they find out that
you're girls‐ Ohhh...?
[MISAKI]
So you're going to give up
before things have even started?
That's not like the
Manager I know at all.
[SATSUKI] But I‐
[MISAKI]
I know that what I'm saying may
sound selfish, but... I don't
WANT to quit.
[SATSUKI]
Ahhhhh...
[SUBARU]
Don't worry guys, I'll be
right there with Misa to make
sure she doesn't get hurt.
[MISAKI]
All right, wish us luck.
[HONOKA]
Once she gets a fire under
her, it sure does stay lit,
doesn't it?
[ERIKA]
I like a girl with
determination! Misa'll
find a way to pull this off!
Isn't that right, Manager?
[SATSUKI]
That's right...
[SUBARU]
A‐are you okay? I'm
not too heavy, am I?
[MISAKI] Don't worry, it's fine.
[SUBARU]
You're sure...?
[MISAKI, thinking]
Despite what I told the boss,
it's MY fault we're in this
mess in the first place.
[MISAKI]
The president of Miyabigaoka has
me in his sights, and because of
me, Maid Latte could‐
[JUDGE A] Is everyone ready?
[MISAKI] Uh?
[JUDGE A]
Take your positions...
(aggressive racing)
[ERIKA] Do your best, guys! We
believe in you! Crush 'em!
[HONOKA] The race just started
and Misa's already whipping
[ERIKA] Go get it!
We know you can do it!
[SATSUKI]
Don't push yourselves too hard!
[SARASHINA] L‐O‐V‐E!
Goooo, Misa!!
[ALL] Huh?
[BUTLER E]
I'm dying...
[BUTLER F]
C'mon, man‐ let's switch.
[BUTLER G] I can't go on...
[BUTLER H]
It's too much for me!
[SUBARU] Are you sure you're
doing okay, Misa?
[MISAKI] I'm just fine!
[MISAKI, thinking]
Like I thought, it's hard to
move in this suit,
but if I can just make it up
this hill, we've got this!
[KUROSAKI] That's the spirit!
[SHIROKAWA] Let's do our best
together, Misa!
[SHIROKAWA]
If we're with you, we'll have
the strength of a hundred men!
[KUROSAKI]
With Shiroyan and I
there's no way you'll‐
[KUROSAKI] Ack... ah...
[MISAKI] What the heck
was that about?
[SHIROKAWA] Aaah, Kurotatsu!
[MISAKI & SUBARU]
Uh?!
(BUTLERS freaking out)
[MISAKI] I guess all sorts of
people are participating in this
event, huh?
[SUBARU] So it seems...
[MAN A] You are Number 38.
[MISAKI] (heavy breathing)
[SUBARU] It's amazing how fast
some of the other competitors
are.
[SATSUKI]
Great work, you two!
[ERIKA]
You did awesome, Misaki.
[MISAKI] No, not at all.
[ERIKA] Do your best, Subaru.
[SUBARU]
Would you please stop this
blatant sexual harassment.
[ERIKA]
But you're a guy, so touching
your chest doesn't count as
sexual harassment.
[SUBARU] Of course it counts‐
now please quit touching me!
[YUKIMURA] Hey, Kanou!
[YUKIMURA] You'll let me handle
the next event, right?
[KANOU] It's impossible.
[MISAKI] What are THEY doing
here?!
[YUKIMURA]
How do you know it's impossible
if you won't even let me try?
[KANOU]
I just know.
[ERIKA]
Is something wrong, Misaki?
[MISAKI]
Erika... Eh?
Your glasses... I need to borrow
them right now!
[ERIKA] Huh?
[MAKI]
Those who passed
the first event,
please head to the
gymnasium at once.
[MAKI]
The second event will
soon be underway.
[SUBARU]
Seriously, this is their
school's gymnasium?
[HONOKA]
This place is more like
a sports arena than a gym.
[ERIKA]
I can barely make the two of
them out from up here...
[SATSUKI]
Look at how plush the cushioning
on these seats is...
[YUKIMURA]
This is amazing, KANOU.
[MISAKI] Gah!
[KANOU] Indeed.
[MISAKI]
Those guys are interested
in this kind of job?
[MISAKI]
If they see me,
I'm totally busted!
[KUROSAKI] Yahoo‐!
[SHIROKAWA] We made it too,
Misa‐!
[MAKI]
Once again, I welcome you all.
Congratulations on passing the
first challenge and making it to
the second round.
[MAKI]
I'm sure a few of you were
caught off guard by that rather
strange event.
[SHIROKAWA] Misa
stepped on us...!
[KUROSAKI] (happy pain)
[MAKI]
The purpose of the first
challenge was to test your
earnestness and determination.
[MAKI]
As you may or may not know,
the job of a footman is a
very difficult one.
And because it is difficult, it
requires the strength to keep up
with your peers no matter what.
It is for that reason that
we required all entrants to
have a partner.
[MAKI]
This audition will test your
abilities to work with your
partner,
and assess whether
you can perform as a
full‐fledged footman.
[MAKI]
The assessment shall be made by
myself and the butlers,
and we ask for your cooperation
here at this venue and beyond.
[MAKI]
Now, please allow me to
introduce Miyabigaoka student
council president, Mr. Igarashi.
[BUTLERS] (intrigued)
[MISAKI, thinking] I knew
he'd be around here somewhere!
[MISAKI] Just you watch: I'll
see this through to the end!
[MAKI] And now, let us begin the
next event.
[MISAKI] Get outta my WAYYYYY!
[MAKI] Excellent work.
[BUTLER A] I'm so tired!
[MAKI] The first round, to gauge
your physical strength, is now
complete.
(BUTLERS breathing hard)
(BOTH breathing heavily)
[MISAKI] That the
best they can do?!
[MAKI]
Will all contestants please
change before we begin Round 2.
[MAKI]
You've each been provided with
tailcoats and a uniform.
[MAKI]
Please change into
them within one minute.
[MISAKI & SUBARU] One minute?!
[MISAKI] Are they crazy?!
[MAKI] This challenge will test
the quickness of your thinking
and your reflexes.
[MAKI] Are all
contestants ready?
[MISAKI] Huh?! We have
to change HERE? No way!
[MAKI]
Please note that the two‐person
changing rooms will fall down
once your time is up.
[MISAKI & SUBARU] (freaking out)
[MAKI] And... Begin!
[MISAKI] Th‐this is bad...!
[MISAKI]
Just hurry up, Subaru...
Uh, I mean, MISTER Subaru!
[SUBARU]
I‐I know that, Mister MISAKI!
[SATSUKI] (freaking out)
[ERIKA]
Uh oh. I do not foresee
this ending well.
[HONOKA] MISAKI's fast at
everything, so I'm sure she'll
be fine... but Subaru...
[MAKI] Your time is up.
[SUBARU] (squeal)
[HONOKA] Yep. Called it.
[BUTLERS] (confused adlibs)
[BUTLER H] Huh?
Was that a girl?
[BUTLER I] No way!
[SUBARU] I'm sorry... MISAKI.
[BUTLER K] This audition is
for men only, right?
[BUTLER J] That was a girl!
[BUTLER L] Nobody realized
it till now?!
[KUROSAKI] Oh, crap!!
[SHIROKAWA] (freaking out)
[BUTLER M] I bet those freaks
in the masks are the girls!
(shaking)
[BUTLER H] That makes sense.
They're way too suspicious!
[AOI]
Jeez. I knew these masks
were a stupid idea.
[AOI]
All that hard work for nothing!
[BUTLER A] A guy?
[BUTLER B] Wait, a girl?
[BUTLERS] (confused)
[BUTLER C] Which one is it?
[MISAKI]
Usui and Aoi are here, too?!
[SUBARU]
So that WAS Usui then,
I knew it.
[MISAKI]
Huh? Subaru, you knew
it was them all long?
[AOI] Of course I'm a boy! It's
obvious‐ are you people blind or
something?!
[SUBARU] Not really, I just
[MISAKI]
What kind of reason is that?!
[MAKI] Only males of high school
age or older may participate.
Before we continue I'm afraid I
must ask your gender and age.
[AOI]
I'm a man. And my age is... 14.
[BUTLER D] Dude, you're young!
[BUTLER E] You're in middle
school?!
[MAKI] In that case....
[AOI] Yeah, yeah, I know,
I know‐
I'm disqualified, right?! That's
why I wore that stupid mask!
[MAKI]
I must also ask that
individual over there.
[MAKI]
You are a woman, are you not?
[SUBARU] Yes, I am.
[SUBARU]
I'm sorry.
[MISAKI]
No, no. I'm sorry.
[MAKI]
Very well, both partners are
automatically eliminated.
[MAKI]
Please exit the
premises immediately.
[AOI] Hmph...
[SUBARU] Huh? Misaki?
[AOI] Huh?
[TORA] Say, Maki.
[MAKI] Sir?
[TORA] May I make a suggestion?
Those two were able to make it
this far with a child and a girl
as their partners‐ surely
they must be quite skilled.
[TORA]
It would be a terrible shame to
lose such talented personnel.
[TORA]
Why not let the remaining two
stay and form a new pair?
[TORA] That is... as long as
they both meet the proper
criteria.
[MISAKI] (shocked)
[MAKI]
Very well. Will the remaining
contestants please confirm that
they are indeed qualified?
[USUI]
Seventeen years old.
High‐school student. Male.
[BUTLER A]
The one with the glasses
is a bit suspicious.
[BUTLER B]
If anyone's a girl, it's him!
[MISAKI]
Sixteen years old.
High‐school student.
[USUI] Ah?
[MISAKI] And I am...
[MISAKI] A BOY!
[TORA] (taken aback)
[BOTH] WHOOOOAAA!
Uwahhhhhh!
[SATSUKI & ERIKA]
(shocked)
[USUI] Flat as an ironing board.
(BUTLERS laughing)
[SATSUKI] [ERIKA] Uh...
[BUTLER C] Looks like he was
hoping it really was a girl!
[BUTLER D]
I knew he was a guy all along.
[BUTLER H]
Yeah, it's totally obvious.
[MAKI] Sir.
In that case. We will now
move on to the second round.
[MISAKI]
After an intense first round,
I've now been paired with Usui
of all people.
[USUI]
It must be fate, Mister Misaki.
[TORA]
Hmph! You're an
interestin' girl.
[MISAKI]
See‐ there goes Tora again,
acting all uppity!
[USUI]
You should just glare back at
him. He's staring too much.
[YUKIMURA] Aah! I'm
so scared, Kanou!
[KANOU] Just take a
few deep breaths.
[MISAKI]
Oh, no! YUKIMURA AND KANOU! I'll
just sneak this way...! Ungh...
[MAKI]
And so, we shall now
proceed to Round 2.
[YUKIMURA]
Oh, no! It's starting!
(heavy breathing)
[KANOU]
It's not starting. At least,
not until the next episode.