[MISAKI]
Huh? You made a promise with one
of our customers by mistake?
That's right. It was
a total accident.
[ERIKA]
He's always been so supportive
of me, but one day he caught me
when I was super busy and I kind
of agreed without thinking.
[BOY]
What? You really mean it?!
[ERIKA]
Uh, certainly, Master.
[BOY]
Wahooo!
(ERIKA sighs)
[MISAKI] What exactly
did you agree to?
[ERIKA]
You know that dessert eating
contest event we have this
weekend?
If he wins, I have to go on a
date with him for an entire day.
[MISAKI]
Huh?!
On top of that dating customers
outside of work
is against Maid Latte's rules.
I've really done it now!
[ERIKA]
It's my own fault.
[MISAKI]
Basically, all you have to do is
make sure that customer doesn't
win, right?
[ERIKA] Huh?
[MISAKI] Don't you worry, I can
eat desserts like nobody's
business.
[ERIKA]
Huh? B‐But...
Just leave it to me!
[MISAKI]
I'll be back later.
I don't know if this
disguise is gonna work.
[ERIKA]
Don't worry! With this rock star
disguise no one will be able to
tell who you are!
[MISAKI]
Hey there, Suzuna.
[SUZUNA]
Huh? Huh? Is that...?
The answer is my sister...
[MISAKI'S GHOST]
You win!
[SHIROKAWA]
What the hell are you doing
here, transfer student?
[SHINTANI]
I was in a parfait‐eating
contest at another coffee shop,
and they told me about the event
goin' on here so I thought I'd
come for more free food!
[KUROSAKI]
You dumb ass! Not just anyone
can enter, you've gotta be a
loyal customer, you got me?
[SHIROKAWA & SARASHINA]
Yeah, that's right!
[MISAKI]
I figured the Three Idiots would
show up, but what the hell is
Shintani doing here?!
[ERIKA]
Oh! There he is!
He's way too excited!
[ERIKA] Oh. Good morning, Usui.
[USUI] Morning.
[ERIKA]
It seems like there's gonna be a
good turnout.
Take a look‐ the
hallway's packed.
[MISAKI] Argh! (freaking out)
[ERIKA] Ah!
[ERIKA] Wouldja look at that!
There's certainly are all kinds
of people out there today!
(awkward laughter)
[SATSUKI]
Ladies and gentlemen! A sweet
chiffon cake with a hint of
English tea...
[SATSUKI]
A lovely frosted chocolate
cupcake...
[SATSUKI]
And a divinely decadent
chocolate sponge cake!
[MAIDS]
Apologies for the wait, Masters!
[GIRL A]
How cute!
[GIRL B]
These look delicious!
[MISAKI]
Usui made these?
Sure, I knew they'd be good,
but I can't believe he'd make
something so cute...
[SATSUKI] Excellent work, Usui!
Your desserts are so cute and
delicious, and everyone loves
them!
[USUI]
I'm glad to hear it.
You really ought to think about
making this into a career!
[USUI]
Oh no, I couldn't possibly!
I'm happy with it as a hobby.
(forced laughs)
[SEN‐CHAN & MOCCHI]
Give us some of your skill!
[SHINTANI]
(chomp) Yummy!
[MISAKI]
I'll figure something out once
I've taken out Erika's number
one fan.
[SARASHINA]
I WILL win this‐ no matter what!
[SHIROKAWA]
I'm gonna get that "reward" they
promised...
[KUROSAKI]
I‐I can't go on!
[SARASHINA] What?!
[SHIROKAWA] Kurotatsu!
The maids will have to punish
any Master who leaves food on
his plate, kay?
[KUROSAKI]
Punish me?
I'm sorry. I give up.
[BOTH]
He's going straight for the
punishment?!
[SUBARU]
Oh, really? I'm very sorry, sir,
but...
Please stand still for
just a moment, okay?
[SHIROKAWA]
She's gonna flick
him in the head?
[SUBARU]
Here goes...
Flick!
Masters, please be sure to leave
nothing on your plates
or else I'll have to
punish you as well.
[BOTH] Yes, ma'am!
[MISAKI]
I'm starting to get full...
[SHIROKAWA]
Thanks for the food. But I quit.
[SARASHINA]
Me, too.
[SUBARU]
Three contestants remaining!
[USUI]
As I expected.
You're increasing the
size of the desserts now?
Usui, you're a bit of
a sadist, aren't you?
[USUI]
Well, this makes it...
more interesting, right?
[HONOKA]
Smooch! Smooch!
[SHINTANI]
Ahhh... (chomp)
[SATSUKI]
If we're having cake,
then strawberries and cream is
the only way to go!
I call this one the "Maid's
Devotion Shortcake"!
Please, eat with love!
[MISAKI]
They bring this
monstrosity out now?!
Sure, it tastes good, but all
this cream and sponge cake is
really filling!
[BOY]
(choking)
[MISAKI]
(gasp) That means...!
I‐I'm finished!
[SATSUKI] Masters Hinata and
Bisanki... have completely
finished!
(PATRONS cheering)
[SATSUKI]
Congratulations!
[MISAKI]
No regrets...
[SATSUKI]
Now then, our two finalists will
move on to the championship
round!
[SHINTANI]
Huh? I get to eat even more?
[SATSUKI]
Oh my! Looks like this Master
still hasn't had his fill!
[SHINTANI]
I haven't had anywhere near
enough!
[SATSUKI]
Okay, please allow me to explain
the rewards for today's
competition.
[SATSUKI] The first reward is
some home‐made, MAID‐made
cookies!
[MISAKI] Cookies, huh?
[SATSUKI] The second reward is
two coupons for a free "Maids'
Special Lunch!"
[MISAKI] Lunch tickets, huh?
[SATSUKI]
And the third is a ticket for a
commemorative photo with your
favorite maid!
[MISAKI]
Oh. We're doing that too?
[SARASHINA]
Dammit! That's the whole reason
we entered!
By the way, Master, which maid
do you intend to take your
picture with if you win?
[SHINTANI]
Huh? Doesn't matter to me,
anyone is fine.
[SATSUKI]
Well then, please choose the
maid you'd like from this list.
[SATSUKI]
If the maid listed is not here
today, you'll receive a ticket
you can use at a later date.
[SHINTANI]
Uh, in that case, I guess I'll
go with...
[SHINTANI] Misa!
[MISAKI] Gahhhhh!
[SHINTANI]
That's the same name
of the girl I like!
[SATSUKI]
My, what a happy coincidence!
Well, Master Hinata, you appear
to be ready to go.
How about you, Master Bisanki,
are you ready? Huh?
[SATSUKI, thinking]
Misa! What is she doing?!
[MISAKI, thinking]
I can't let anyone else from
my school know about my secret!
The winner will be whoever
can finish our "extra special
sweets" the fastest.
However, please do not force
yourself too much. Oh?
[MISAKI]
I accept the challenge!
(sigh) I see. So she's
going to keep going, huh?
[SATSUKI]
Can't we take it a little easy
on her? She looks like she's in
pain...
[USUI]
That wouldn't be
any fun, would it?
[SATSUKI] Oh?
[USUI] The finale will be
something they'll never forget.
[USUI]
I'm going to drive them wild
with the ultimate dessert.
[SATSUKI]
Woot woot!
And...
Congratulations to our winner,
Master Hinata!
(cheering)
[SHINTANI] I did it!
[MISAKI]
I can't believe we had to eat
a WHOLE cake for the finale...!
Misa...
Why'd "Mister Bisanki" go
and push himself so hard?
[SUBARU]
You already accomplished what
you wanted, didn't you?
[ERIKA]
Y‐You found us out?
[HONOKA]
It's a decent disguise, but it's
way too conspicuous.
[ERIKA]
Misa didn't do anything wrong!
It was because of me, it's my
fault!
The manager will be happy to
hear your explanation later.
[ERIKA]
Okay...
I'm so glad to see that you
enjoyed your food so thoroughly!
[SHINTANI]
Well, everything was
delicious! Huh?
[SATSUKI]
Master, would it be all right if
I asked for your opinion on the
sweets that you sampled today?
[SHINTANI]
Huh? Uh, sure.
[MISAKI]
Ugh, dammit. My stomach's
killing me.
[MISAKI]
I've been laying here for 20
minutes and I still can't move.
[MISAKI]
What should I do?
[USUI]
What do you want to do?
[MISAKI]
Uh! Oh... Usui!
What are you‐?! (gagging)
Just be a good little girl
and try not to throw up while
talking, okay?
You really were an
idiot today, Misa.
[USUI] If it hurts that much,
just lie down.
[MISAKI] No.
[USUI] How about you rest your
head on my legs?
[MISAKI] No thank you!
[USUI] Really?
[MISAKI] Huh?
[USUI]
If you don't like that,
I can find some other,
more creative way
to punish you, Misa.
[MISAKI]
Wha?!
[USUI]
Hey. This isn't fun at all.
[MISAKI]
Look, I don't have the strength
to keep you entertained right
now.
[MISAKI]
Just leave me alone for a bit.
[USUI] Hmmm...
[USUI]
Hey... Were you trying
to get fat? Uh... oh?
[MISAKI]
HEY! Watch where you're
touching!
[USUI]
Huh? That was your stomach,
right?
[MISAKI] You son of a‐!
[USUI] You sure did eat a lot,
didn't you?
[USUI] Well, now! If you eat
that much, you'll get nice and
round in no time!
[MISAKI] Shut up! Stupid
[MISAKI]
Aghhhhh! I can burn off those
calories with no trouble!
[USUI]
(laughter) That's Misa the
fighting maid for you.
Shut up! You're always saying
weird things just to mess with
me!
[USUI]
I thought this might be my
chance to finally put some
MEAT on you.
[MISAKI]
Shut up, you perverted alien!
You don't care about other
people's worries at all! (gasp)
You just... You always...
[MISAKI]
Forget it. You see through
everything, don't you?
[MISAKI]
Dammit.
Did you just do something?
[USUI]
Nope. You must've imagined it.
[MISAKI]
Oh...
[SAKURA]
Misaki! Wanna go to an
all‐you‐can‐eat dessert buffet?!
[SHIZUKO] All‐you‐can‐eat?
[MISAKI] Desserts?
[MISAKI]
Sorry, I don't think I'll be
wanting anything sweet for a
while.
[SAKURA] Huh? Don't tell
me you're on a diet!
[SHIZUKO] This buffet could get
quite dangerous, Sakura.
[SAKURA]
Well, maybe next time!
(giggling)
[SHIZUKO]
We shall invite you again and
again.
[USUI]
The others there thought it was
strange, too.
[USUI]
Why would you want to win so
badly? What's in it for you?
[MISAKI]
Huh? Don't tell me EVERYBODY
knew!
[USUI]
Thinking you could seriously
fool anyone is just like you...
[SHINTANI] Misaki!
[MISAKI] Gah! Shintani!
[SHINTANI] Come with me.
[MISAKI] What's with you all
of a sudden? Shintani...
[SHINTANI] Just come on.
[MISAKI, thinking] Don't
tell me HE knew, too?!
[SHINTANI] Do you
play the guitar?
[MISAKI, thinking]
Here it comes!
[SHINTANI] Do you like to wear
all‐black clothing, like some
kind of crow?
[MISAKI] No, no, no!
[SHINTANI]
Is see. Then that must've been
someone else, huh?
Oh, Misa! Do you know
anything 'bout maid cafes?
[MISAKI]
No, I don't! Never heard of'em
before!
[SHINTANI]
Oh, yeah? I went to one for the
first time
the other day and
was so surprised!
But I thought it was the kinda
place that a girl'd enjoy even
more!
[MISAKI] Huh?
[SHINTANI]
I got two tickets to eat there
for free,
so how 'bout we go, my treat?!
The food there is great!
Whaddya say‐ Let's go
to Maid Latte together!
[MISAKI]
Huh?!
[DAUGHTER]
Let's go here!
[MISAKI, thinking]
This is the only way
to settle this!
[SATSUKI]
All right, let's go over the
plan one more time.
[SATSUKI] First, Misa and Hinata
come to the shop.
[SHINTANI] La, la! La, la!
[SATSUKI] Misa, you get
up and pretend to leave.
Then, you hurry and change
into your maid outfit,
disguising yourself so he
doesn't recognize you.
[SATSUKI] You take the picture,
and mission accomplished, 'kay!
[ERIKA] I'll take your picture!
[SATSUKI]
I've got the perfect disguise
for you, so I'll make sure to
have it ready by then.
[MISAKI]
Thank you very much.
And... I'm sorry...
about all this.
[SATSUKI]
Oh? Misa, I know that,
in your own way,
you always keep Maid Latte's
best interests at heart.
But there's a reason you have to
do this, right?
[MISAKI] Yeah.
[SATSUKI]
Then it can't be helped.
After all, you're one of
our best workers!
[SATSUKI]
Come on now,
don't make that face.
Hurry up and get to work.
[MISAKI] Yes, ma'am.
As always, our manager is so
disgustingly sweet that it gives
me heartburn.
[ALL] Uh...
[HONOKA] See you all tomorrow.
[ERIKA]
There she is‐ Dark Honoka
appears!
Why are you taggin' along,
Takumi? This was supposed to be
a date with just me an' Misa!
And just so we're clear,
I ain't payin' for ya, got it?!
[USUI]
That's just like you, Sanshita.
Such a cheapskate.
[MISAKI, thinking]
That Usui... He invited himself,
saying he wanted to help.
[MISAKI, thinking]
I don't know why he'd want to
come‐ it's not like anything
exciting's going to happen...
[ERIKA]
Very well, please enjoy, Master.
If you need anything from me,
please do not hesitate to ask.
[ERIKA] Smackdown!
[MISAKI, thinking]
Thank you, Erika!
[HONOKA] Sorry to keep you
waiting, Young Lady.
[MISAKI, thinking] I'm glad we
did this today.
[DAUGHTER] Wow, there's my
omelette!
[MISAKI] We don't get many of
our regular customers on days of
[DAUGHTER] It looks
delicious. Yay!
[MISAKI] so only Usui knows I
work as a maid here.
[MISAKI, thinking]
As long as he just keeps his
mouth shut, everything should go
fine.
[SHINTANI]
Whoa, today they have a kid's
lunch?!
[SHINTANI]
I wonder if they'll let me trade
my free coupon for this instead!
[USUI] Not gonna happen.
[SHINTANI] I'm not askin'
you, Takumi!
[SHINTANI] And what are you even
doin' here hangin' around with
Misaki, as if it were natural?!
(Usui murmuring)
[MISAKI] Sma‐Smack! This isn't a
place for carrying on and
fooling around!
[BOYS] Ah!
[MISAKI & YOUNG MISAKI]
Please mind your manners!
[MISAKI]
What are you giggling about?
And why are you dressed like
that? Where's your school
uniform?
[SHINTANI]
Oh, this is for my part‐time
job. I got my uniform all wet.
[MISAKI]
You have a part‐time job?!
[SHINTANI]
(laughing) I figured you'd be
surprised most of all!
[SHINTANI]
Even Ol' Shintani can work at a
gas station. You bet'cha!
[USUI]
Using gasoline to pay the bills?
I doubt you'll get much MILEAGE
out of that.
[SHINTANI]
What're you sayin'? I got no
idea what you're talkin' about.
[USUI]
Ah, my bad. I forgot you weren't
very smart.
Hey look you, I'm a dependable
guy who can hold down a job!
[SHINTANI] That's right! You
should come by and see me some
time, Misaki.
[MISAKI] Uh...
I'd like you to see how
I'm different from when
we were kids, what I look
like hard at work.
[MISAKI]
I can already see how much
you've changed without having to
visit you at work.
[SHINTANI]
Oh. That's too bad.
Back then you were always so
lazy... staring off into space,
never studying, never
exercising, and the only
thing you were good at was
pigging out.
(SHINTANI chuckles)
[MISAKI] And you were
a huge liar.
[YOUNG MISAKI]
Hey Yoh, are you eating candy
again?
[YOUNG SHINTANI] No, I'm not.
[YOUNG MISAKI] It's bad to
tell lies!
[YOUNG SHINTANI] I'm not lying.
[YOUNG MISAKI] You said you
wouldn't eat any more today!
[YOUNG SHINTANI] No, I didn't.
[USUI] Pathetic.
[SHINTANI]
Shut up, that was a long time
ago!
[SHINTANI] I'd never lie‐
[MISAKI] Yes, you've changed.
[MISAKI]
And you're a lot more passionate
than I thought... Yoh.
[MISAKI]
Maybe Yoh isn't the only one
who's changed...
[SHINTANI] It was thanks to you,
Misaki!
[MISAKI] Uh?
It's because you were always
such a hard little worker who
always did her best!
[SHINTANI]
And you were so kind. I thought
you were the best.
[USUI]
Wow. That's very sparkly.
[MISAKI]
Cut it out, Shintani! You're
romanticizing things too much!
[MISAKI]
Some people called me obnoxious
and said they hated me!
That's cuz they were just tryin'
to hide how embarrassed they
were.
[SHINTANI]
Cuz when you smile, you're
really cute!
[MISAKI]
(embarrassed) Wh‐What are
you talking about?
[SHINTANI]
It's true. Mah said the same
thing, too.
[MISAKI]
"Mah"? Oh, I remember him...
[SHINTANI]
He and Shige came over to my
place one time just so they
could see you.
[MISAKI]
Huh? Why'd they come
so far just to‐
[USUI]
Oh. I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
[MISAKI, thinking]
What's with this strange
tension?
[SHINTANI] Misaki?
[MISAKI] Huh?
[MISAKI]
Uh, yeah, anyway,
good luck with your
job and do your best!
Mhm. Thanks! By the way,
I heard you've got a
part‐time job, too.
[MISAKI] Huh?
[SHINTANI] What kinda job is it?
[MISAKI, thinking]
What a complete mishandling of
the conversation!
[SHINTANI]
Do you mean, like at a
convenience store or a
restaurant?
[MISAKI] I‐It's just... just a
regular job!
[MISAKI]
Yeah, uh, it's in the dining
industry.
Then you're a waitress! I'd like
to see that! I bet you're great!
[MISAKI]
It's no big deal, nothing
to see, really!
Huh, why not? Takumi, you'd
like to see it too, right?
[SHINTANI]
Or, wait, have you maybe
seen it already?
[MISAKI, thinking]
Oh crap! If Usui says he has,
their rivalry will make Shintani
even more curious!
[MISAKI]
Please...
Lie!
[SHINTANI] Huh?
(MISAKI gasps)
Hey Misaki. Is something the
matter?
[MISAKI]
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
[SHINTANI]
I wonder if she's okay.
[USUI]
This is someone she doesn't want
to lie to, at all... really...
[SHINTANI]
You say somethin'
over there, Takumi?
[USUI] Snoooore.
(SHINTANI grunts)
[SHINTANI]
I was in an accident way back.
Both my mom and my dad died,
[SHINTANI]
and for a while, I didn't know
what was goin' on.
My relatives got together and
everyone was cryin'... but it's
like it was all happenin' far
away.
[SHINTANI]
I kinda... muddled my way
through every day...
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
So, my grandpa is like, "Come
live with me,"
but there's no convenience
stores or supermarkets nearby,
so I don't wanna go.
He says if we live together I
won't be lonely anymore, but I'm
not lonely at all, not one bit.
'Sides if I'm alone I can eat
all the candy I want. Maybe
he'll just go away soon.
[GRANDPA]
You're talkin' that stupid stuff
again, Hinata?!
[GRANDPA] You weren't at home,
so I've been lookin' for ya!
[YOUNG SHINTANI] Grandpa!
[GRANDPA]
It's time you stop
tryin' to act tough.
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
I'm not tryin' to act
tough you liar!
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
I'm not lonely or sad by myself,
so just hurry up and go back to
Grandma and leave me alone‐
(YOUNG SHINTANI crying)
[YOUNG MISAKI]
If you're sad or you're lonely,
you absolutely can't lie about
it, okay Yoh?!
[YOUNG SHINTANI]
(big wailing) Mom! Daddy!
Once I started crying, I felt
everything I'd been holding
inside burst like a dam and the
tears just wouldn't stop.
[SHINTANI]
When he saw that, my Gramps
started crying, too.
[SHINTANI]
Misaki probably doesn't
remember, but I still remember
it like it was yesterday.
(YOUNG SHINTANI crying)
[YOUNG MISAKI] I'm sorry I
smacked your cheeks, Yoh.
[SHINTANI]
Her words... The smile she gave
me when I stopped crying...
Ever since then, she's
been the girl I've loved.
[USUI]
Is that your declaration
of war, Yoh?
[SHINTANI] Mm...
[SHINTANI]
If you feel the same as I do...
you bet it is.
[MISAKI, thinking]
"Please, just tell a lie"?
For me to think something like
that, just to protect myself...
Becoming the "tyrant president"
and working at Maid Latte...
those are both decisions that
I made.
[SATSUKI]
Oh, Misa! That was fast.
Weren't you going to escape
during lunch?
[MISAKI]
Ma'am!
[MISAKI, thinking]
Is this really something
I have to hide...?
Misa, lookie, lookie! See, I
told you it was the perfect
disguise, didn't I?
[SATSUKI]
See? If you put this on, no one
will ever know it's you!
[MISAKI] Manager! I've...!
(BABY crying)
[SATSUKI]
Oh, my. A baby started crying.
I wonder if we have anything
to calm it down. Let's see...
[SHINTANI]
Oh, look you're up high!
There, there! Your mom will
be back from the toilet soon.
(BABY giggling)
[SHINTANI]
Look at you, kiddo! I thought
you were cryin', but now you're
laughin', huh?
[SHINTANI]
(chuckles) That's a nice smile!
[MOTHER]
I'm sorry for the trouble.
[SHINTANI]
Not at all. See ya.
[MOTHER]
I'm sorry.
[SHINTANI]
Huh? Takumi? (sigh)
[MISAKI]
I've brought your lunch.
Huh?
[MISAKI]
Please have a seat...
Enjoy your meal.
[SHINTANI]
Misaki, is that... you?
[MISAKI]
My name is Misa.
[SHINTANI]
But you're Misaki... right?
[MISAKI]
Shhhh...
[SHINTANI] Misaki,
you're "Misa"?!
[MISAKI] Uhagh!
[SHINTANI] So THIS is where you
work?! HERE?!
[MISAKI] M‐Master, could you be
a bit quieter, please?
[SHINTANI]
You should've just said so!
What'd you go an' lie about it
for?!
[USUI] Excuse me.
[MISAKI & SHINTANI] Uh?
[USUI]
Pardon me, Master... But please
refrain from laying your hands
on our maids.
[USUI]
Here, as an apology
for my rudeness.
[USUI]
Isn't it delicious?
[SHINTANI] Shrry...
[MISAKI] Uh...
[USUI]
You there. Causing this
disruption shows your
inexperience as a maid.
[MISAKI]
M‐My apologies, sir.
[USUI]
Come with me. You will need to
be punished immediately.
[GIRL S]
I didn't know Maid Latte
had these events.
[GIRL B]
Maid cafés are always so much
fun.
[USUI]
Weren't you... supposed to
disguise yourself?
[MISAKI]
Yeah... but I couldn't...
I just couldn't lie
to him like that.
[USUI]
Well, that's more like our
student council president.
[MISAKI]
Uh? You came through for me
again, didn't you? Thank you.
[USUI] Ayuzawa,
you really are...
[MISAKI] Hm?
[USUI]
Cruel, aren't you?
[MISAKI] Usui...
[SHINTANI] Misaki!
[MISAKI]
Shintani! Why are
you back here?
[SHINTANI]
Just now, Usui came out of the
back entrance, didn't he?
[SHINTANI]
Does that mean the two of you
work here together?
[MISAKI]
Usui does, but only sometimes...
[SHINTANI]
Misaki, that outfit really looks
good on you!
Dressin' up all pretty like
that... I really mean it!
I mean it!
[USUI]
I won't warn you again.
Touch Ayuzawa again...
And next time, I'll bite.
[USUI] Keep that in mind.
(dog growling)
[SHINTANI] Huh?
[MISAKI]
What is up with these two?
[HONOKA]
She's so smart, and yet so
stupid at the same time.
Really makes you want to give
her a kick in the ass, huh?
(evil laugh)
[SUBARU]
Did something happen?
[SATSUKI]
Honoka's just busy thinking
happy thoughts
about Misaki. I think...
[SATSUKI]
This is rather sudden, but how
about we give everyone at Maid
Latte their own way of speaking?
What shall we add to your
sentences?
[SATSUKI]
Honoka can add "ho" to her
sentences. Ho!
[ERIKA]
Then I'm Erika, so I add "eri"?
[SUBARU]
Erika, nice use of the
interrogative, su!
[GON‐CHAN]
I'm going to force this into
conversation, gon!
[SHIZUKO]
We'll get used to it if we keep
using them, sayu!
[SEN‐CHAN]
Don't you think it'll get pretty
tough, sen?
[MOCCHI]
It might be fun, mocchi!
[SATSUKI]
Good job, everyone!
Okay, Misa and Usui,
do the preview like that, satsu.
[MISAKI]
Huh? Ma'am, I can't do it, mi!
Usui, I'm counting on you, mi!
[USUI] Next time, Misa's
mom drops some fruit
and we'll see the story of
the Magical Girl MEI‐Dos, usu.