Guh!
Ugh!
AH!
Oohhh!
Aaahh!
(groaning in pain)
[PUNK A]
H‐hey... We give up
already, Aratake!
[PUNK B]
Yeah, we get how tough you are!
[PUNK C]
We're sorry, man.
We weren't tryin' to start
nothin' by starin' at you.
[PUNK D]
Yeah, everyone around already
knows you're the number one guy
at Seisen Jr. High!
[ARATAKE]
Then I guess it's about time
that I introduce myself.
[PUNK D]
Huh? To who?
Seisen Junior High's
former legend...
[ARATAKE]
The guy they call the
Tornado, the White Demon:
Naoya Shirokawa!
Finally, I thought
class would never end!
Today's Girls in
Glasses Day, isn't it?
Let's hurry up
and go, go, go!
[SHIROKAWA]
Why don't you try
runnin', dumbass?!
[KUROSAKI]
All right! It's a race!
[SHIROKAWA]
You guys couldn't keep up!
[SARASHINA]
What did you say?!
(TRIO continue
taunting each other)
[KONDO]
Aratake...
It's just a coincidence.
That small fry couldn't
possibly be the White Demon.
[TAHARA]
Looks like he dropped somethin'.
Let's follow him
just to be sure.
[TRIO]
Misaaaaa! We're back!
[MISAKI]
Welcome back, Masters.
[ARATAKE]
What the‐?! What's that
weird‐lookin shop?
[OKITA]
It's one of those things,
ain't it? Y'know, a maid café.
That thing's freaking me out.
No way in hell am I going in a
place like that!
It's gotta be someone else
who has the same name.
[KUROSAKI] You're paying today,
right, Shiroyan?
[ARATAKE] Huh?!
Huh? What're you talking
about, Kurotatsu?
[KONDO]
Wait, did he just say...?
[KUROSAKI] Cuz it's
your turn, Shiroyan!
[SHIROKAWA] Huh? ME?
[Naoe]
So... then that
really is him...?
(grunting)
There's no way
this can be right!
(school bell ringing)
Misa's off today,
so I guess we'll
do THAT, huh?
Oh, you mean the
legendary super‐speed
training!
We'll have our Maid
Latte points saved
up soon enough!
[SHIROKAWA]
This time for sure, we'll get
a picture taken with Misa.
[YUKIMURA]
Someone please help me!
[TRIO]
Huh?
Oh! Shirokawa, Sarashina,
and Kurosaki! (panting)
[KUROSAKI]
What are you doing,
Vice President?
Whoa! I didn't recognize
you at all, man!
Hey, look, you're dressed
up like a girl again.
Are you sure you're
really a boy?
Of course I'm a boy!
I didn't want to‐ he
forced me to wear this!
[HAGIMOTO]
Yukimura, don't say anything,
just put on this girl's uniform,
and come to my house‐ QUICK!
Huh? What do I have to that for?
[UTSUMI]
Hagimoto's mom has been hounding
him for like, four years to get
a girlfriend. She's crazy!
[UTSUMI] So put that on and
pretend to be his girl. 'Kay?
[YUKIMURA] Huh?!
Please, I'm begging you!
That's what happened, I swear!
[SHIROKAWA]
Sorry, but we don't really
have time for this.
[YUKIMURA]
Ngh! Wait a second!
You've gotta help me!
[SHIROKAW]
I'm tellin' ya, We're busy.
[KUROSAKI]
What do you want us to
do about it?
[YUKIMURA]
I'd at least like to change!
Please get me some clothes
before someone sees me!
[KUROSAKI]
Forget about it.
Don't say that! Please,
I'll do anything!
You look cute, so what's the
problem? It's not like anyone's
gonna recognize you.
[ARATAKE]
She's "cute," huh?
That's a careless
comment to make.
What the?
[YUKIMURA] Ah!
[TRIO] Huh?
[ARATAKE] I'll just hold onto
this for you.
If you want your
girlfriend back,
then you'll have to
come fight me for her!
As the legendary Senior of
Seisen Junior High School...
[TRIO]
Huh?
Did you find him?
No, no sign of him..
But I told my mom I'd
be bringing my girlfriend
over tonight!
What are you two doing
in the hallway?
Argh! I, uh, I forgot to
separate the recyclables
from the trash!
Whoa! And I have to write
the script for tomorrow's
school broadcast.
[BOTH]
See you later!
[MISAKI]
Huh? Where'd these come from?
President?
Uh? Usui!
Did you strip
search someone?
D‐Don't be ridiculous!
Of course I didn't! (grumbling)
[USUI]
If you wanted to strip someone,
all you had to do was ask me.
[MISAKI]
I'm telling you, I didn't
strip anyone! Stupid pervert.
[TRIO]
GLOOOM...
Huh? What's wrong with you guys?
President...
What's with this weird
aura around them?
The student vice president's
been kidnapped.
Huh?
Crows are scary!
[MISAKI]
So then that school
uniform was Yukimura's?
Miss President,
you forced him to‐
Enough with the
stripping already!
And? What was with
those guys earlier?
We were their seniors,
we knew them back
in junior high when
we were their
upperclassmen.
And when they said "White
Demon" we recognized'em
right away, right?
Huh?
Yeah, what was that all about?
Shiroyan, are you
the "White Demon"?
You got it! How do
you like me now?!
Oh. The legend
himself, huh?
What kind of a
reaction is that?!
I didn't know Seisen Jr. High
had such wimpy delinquents,
guess that explains a lot.
[USUI] Mhm.
What's that
s'posed to mean?!
Still, delinquent or not,
he said he wasn't gonna
fight anymore.
All cuz his mommy was
getting on him about it.
Dude, you know how
scary my mom can be!
True, if you stare right at
her, you see your life flash
before your eyes...
So that means you have
no intention of fighting
them, right?
Nah, I'm gonna
go have some fun!
Wanna come take cosplay
pictures with us?
No way.
[MISAKI]
I have to go help
Yukimura, I guess.
[SARASHINA]
You "guess"?
[USUI]
It looks more normal
than I expected.
Yeah, I thought it'd
be all broken down
and covered in graffiti
or something like that.
What kind of school is that?
Somebody here told me
there have been fewer
delinquents around
since we graduated.
Huh? Really?
Well? Where did
they take Yukimura?
Hm? I dunno! Ha!
I dunno either!
I've got an idea.
How about I break your
thumbs clean off your hands?
[SHIROKAWA] Huh?
[MISAKI] Sarashina, do it!
[SHIROKAWA & KUROSAKI] NOOO!
[SARASHINA] Shiroyan! Kurotatsu!
I can't do it!
[AOI]
What do you idiots think you're
doing in front of my school?
You're embarrassing me.
Is that you Aoi?!
So you go to Seisen Jr. High?
So what if I do? Look,
just go away already.
You're making a big
scene out here.
Is it Aoi?
AH! Uh, yeah, but,
uh, that is...
That's Akanoske Aoi, 14
years old‐ isn't that right,
Miss President?
[MISAKI] Yeah, yeah!
[AOI]
I can't be seen with you guys...
[MISAKI]
Hey, wait! There's something
I need to ask you real quick.
[AOI]
Yeah, I know him. Aratake, he's
a third year student, right?
He's made a name for himself,
now he's the head of some
other delinquents.
Still, there aren't as many
as there used to be around
here lately...
I feel like I've seen
him before. Weird.
Akanoske Aoi, right?
Maybe we've run into
him at Maid Latte or
something.
Before I enrolled, apparently
there was a band of delinquents
that caused all sorts of
trouble, but now they've more or
less disbanded, and get into a
few isolated fights.
That's beside the point!
What's the school going
to do about this!
[USUI]
Alright, alright. Yukimura
should be our number one
priority now, right?
[USUI]
It's getting pretty late...
Their secret hideout!
[YUKIMURA]
H‐hello? Is someone there?
Why is this happening to
me in the first place?
What should I do? I'm tied
up and my bag and cellphone
are back at school.
As if that's not cruel
enough, people keep
mistaking me for a girl!
(door kicked open)
(teeth chattering,
wincing from fear)
Jeez. I told these guys
not to be so rough.
E‐excuse me‐
Don't move! I'm not lettin'
you get away, understand?
[YUKIMURA]
Please wait! Just tell me what‐
[ARATAKE]
This isn't about you.
Just keep quiet and nothin'
will happen to you.
But at least tell me‐
The one I'm after is the
White Demon. Even he...
is bound to go back to his
old self if I've got his girl.
I'm telling you, you've
made a mistake! I'm not
a girl at all! Look!
I'll prove it to you!
Idiot!
[ARATAKE]
What're you doin?!
You wanna die, you crazy woman?!
What are you tryin' to do?
I'm not a woman either!
A woman shouldn't go
showing her body like that!
Also, there's somethin' else
that's really been bothering me.
You talk WAY too much like
a guy, you know that?!
Would it kill you to try and
sound a little more lady‐like?!
Look, just sit there
and shut up!
Uh...
[YUKIMURA]
But I...
AM a boy though...
[MISAKI]
Jeez! If you had a clue,
you should've said so in
the first place!
[SHIROKAWA]
Well, it was our secret hideout,
so I had to keep it secret.
[KUROSAKI]
And it was well‐known throughout
the neighborhood as a bad‐ass
delinquent hangout.
Then it wasn't much of a
"secret" hideout, was it?
Are you sure about this?
It's not like we can just stroll
into their hideout,
whether it's secret or not...
That's right, we're
still in our uniforms.
There's the risk that
bad rumors about Seika High
could start floating around
if we're not super careful.
Then you're going to go all
the way home and change?
But by the
time you managed to regroup it
would be nighttime, so why don't
you just leave already?!
[MISAKI]
At this point, shouldn't we
just go the police instead?
[SHIROKAWA]
Uh? That's all right. If we go
to Seisen, we can get everything
straightened out ourselves.
[SHIROKAWA]
All right everybody, let's go!
[KUROSAKI & SARASHINA]
Bounce! Bounce!
[MISAKI]
H‐hey! You're still wearing your
school uniforms!
I swear, you guys are completely
hopeless. Fine, I'll help..
[SHIROKAWA]
"Maid Sama!" will be back...
[KUROSAKI]
after this short break.
[TRIO]
Woo‐hoo!
[SHIROKAWA]
Oh, a Misa doll!
[KUROSAKI] Nice!
[SARASHINA] I want one!
[MISAKI] Shut up!
[TRIO]
Okay...
[AOI]
I told you to keep your filthy
paws offa me!
I'm not some cheap broad you
can touch whenever you like.
[SHIROKAWA]
What're you talkin'
about, dammit?
[KUROSAKI]
That's goin' a bit far,
don't ya think?
[USUI] YOO!
What the hell do you
punks think you're doing?
Get your hands off my girl.
Or I'll friggin' kill ya!
What'd you say?
You got a problem? Let's
throw down right here!
[MISAKI] Hold it right there!
That girl's with me! If
somethin's up, then‐ (crunch)
[MISAKI]
Sorry. I bit my tongue.
CUT! What are you doing?!
It's an easy line‐
quit screwing it up!
Sorry. I don't have what
it takes to be an actress...
What're we doin anyway?
Isn't it obvious‐
we're playin' delinquent!
This way, people will
think we're just acting
out a scene from a movie.
In other words, no one
will pay attention...
[AOI] This way we can go stroll
right into that hideout without
any problems, right?
[KUROSAKI]
I guess‐ but did we really hafta
do those stupid lines?
[MISAKI]
Also, where'd you
get these clothes?
[SARASHINA]
I'm telling you, I've
seen this guy somewhere‐
[AOI]
Shut up! Quit your complaining!
Just hurry up and
do this so we can go!
(chuckling)
What's up, Shiroyan?
(laughing)
Nothin' at all.
Don't get all sappy and
sentimental on me now,
Shiroyan.
(munching)
It's embarrassing.
[ARATAKE]
The White Demon...
[KUROSAKI]
You went and got
ANOTHER action figure?
[SHIROKAWA]
Hah! This one's rare,
so don't ya dare touch it!
[OKITA] I pass.
[NAOE] Seriously, again?
[MISAKI]
So how are we supposed
to get inside?
We have to hurry and help
Yukimura before they kill him!
[SUZUNA] Is that you Sis?
[MISAKI] Suzuna!
[SARASHINA]
Is that your little sister?
[SUZUNA]
Thank you for always
looking after my sister.
Are you off to give
someone the smackdown?
[MISAKI]
NO! Look it says on the sign!
[MISAKI] We're filming,
all right?! Filming!
(ALL agreeing)
[SUZUNA]
It looks like fun. I wanna
try playing the final boss
or something.
Look, Suzuna, just go
home. It's dangerous.
Then how about I play a
hitman or an assassin instead?
I told you, it's not
that kind of story!
Fine, then take these
snacks if you want.
They're frozen pot stickers
I won over at the mall.
How're we supposed to eat
something that's FROZEN?!
Frozen pot stickers should
not be taken lightly.
[SUZUNA]
The taste of the meat and
vegetables is locked in
at a temperature of minus
60 degrees Celsius,
and they're so delicious that
even a five‐star Chinese
restaurant couldn't...
Aratake, there's no way
this guy's gonna show!
Yeah, it's been two years since
anyone's called him the White
Devil, though, hasn't it?
[PUNK A]
Yo, look, he's cryin'!
[PUNK B]
(laughing) What a wuss!
[PUNK C] You were all big
and bad before, what happened?
[SHIROKAWA] What're you
assholes doing?
[PUNKS] Huh?
[KUROSAKI]
Yeah, that guy's from
our school all right.
[SHIROKAWA]
Unforgivable!
Bein' a bully is SO uncool.
[PUNK B] What's this idiot
talkin' about?
[KUROSAKI]
Don't worry, he's just
talking some smack.
Criminal scum.
Come at me then, bro!
[PUNK B]
Huh? What'd you say, dammit?!
[KUROSAKI]
Don't worry, he's just
talking more smack.
[PUNK C]
Don't screw with us!
We'll kick your ass!
(fighting)
[SHIROKAWA]
Hey Kid... what're you spacin'
out for over there?
Your hero has finally
arrived. Try and be a
little more grateful.
The White Demon... will
definitely come after her...
[MISAKI]
She finally went home...
That endless frozen pot
stickers speech, tho.
I guess any sister of
yours couldn't exactly
be "normal" huh?
She sure was pretty.
Now's not the time for this!
That's right‐
we've gotta hurry up
and help Yukimura
before they find out.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
[SATSUKI]
Ah, Misa is that you?!
What's this?! You're
making your own movie?
[MISAKI] Manager!
[SATSUKI]
Oh my, and Aoi's with you too!
Is this the script?
Show me, show me!
Woooow...
ANOTHER interruption?
Delinquents, huh? If you guys're
doing a school drama,
then you have to have
that one line:
"We ain't no rotten
oranges." You know?
[KUROSAKI] "Rotten oranges"?
[SARASHINA] What's that
supposed to mean?
[SHIROKAWA]
It means fruit is most delicious
when it's just been picked.
[KUROSAKI]
Whoa! Then that means we
didn't fully ripen yet!
Hey, Misa, that outfit looks
really good on you. It's so
different that it's awesome!
Awesomely differently cute!
It's not good it's great!
Hey, I know! How about
we do a Delinquent Day
for our next event?
We could call our male
customers "Dude" and the
female ones "Sis"!
[SATSUKI] Honoka and the others
would totally go for it! And
Erika, too!
[AOI] Come on...
[ARATAKE]
Why isn't he here?
[NAOE]
He told everyone he was
retirin' after junior high,
so I guess he doesn't want
anything to do with guys
like us anymore.
I heard he was scared of someone
takin' him on in high school.
That's enough,
you guys.
Shirokawa was Aratake's
upperclassman
who he respected
more than anyone!
You're saying you
wanna get stronger?
[KUROSAKI]
Big talk comin' from a dude
who's crying like a little baby!
[SHIROKAWA]
That's right. First thing you
gotta do is get really crazy!
Listen, it's no good askin'
an idiot like this for‐
Hey! Kurotatsu!
Still, when this guy loses it
he gets about a hundred times
stronger,
that's why they started calling
him the White Demon‐ pretty lame
nickname if you ask me.
[SHIROKAWA]
Shut up, it's cool dammit!
The way I fight is so awesome,
it's like settin' off a tornado
or something!
[ARATAKE] So...
[BOTH]
Huh?
So cool!
[SHIROKAWA] (laughing)
Hey, why don't you come with us?
[AOI] She FINALLY left.
[USUI]
I wonder if Yukimura's
still alive...
[MISAKI]
We have to hurry and help him.
[SAKURA]
There you are, Misaki!
[SHIZUKO]
We heard from Suzuna.
You're doing your own
movie shoot, are you?
Again?
I just want to finish this
and go home!
We wanna help
you too, Misaki!
Feel free to leave
the recording to me.
Uh, no, we've got plenty of
people, so we're fine.
I brought along some props
from the Filmmaking Club.
A sword and a 9 millimeter.
And we've got plenty
of fake blood, too!
Uh, great, but it's not
that kinda story...
[INUYAMA BROTHERS] Master!
Please allow us to help, too!
[SAKURA] Whoa!
[SHIZUKO] You're the Ayuzawa
Cram School, aren't you?
[ICHIROU]
Please cast me as an extra!
I would play an
excellent "Thug A"!
[JIROU]
Then please let me play Thug B!
[SABUROU]
And I'll be Thug C!
[SHIROU]
And I'll be Thug D!
[GOROU]
And I'll be Thug E!
No, you've got it all wrong!
Misaki, I'm pretty sure you've
gotta be cursed or something.
You first years probably don't
know cuz you've never met him,
but Shirokawa was a
really incredible guy.
He was ridiculously tough,
and once he lost his temper,
he was like an animal.
But we were his guys, and he
looked out for us like family.
(chuckling)
If he was so great then why'd
he quit after he left Seisen?
Sounds to me like he's
hiding in the shadows like
a little baby scaredy cat.
[ARATAKE]
Shut your damn mouth!
You guys don't know
anything about him!
You can't handle the
number one spot, can you?
[ARATAKE]
Uh?! (growling)
You shut up, too!
Bastard... I've had
enough of your crap!
[MISAKI]
Where's Yukimura?
[AOI]
I don't have the energy
to look for him anymore.
[USUI]
Do we have enough strength
left to save him?
[SHIROKAWA]
Hey, it's over this way.
[KONDO]
You're so obsessed with the past
that it's split us all apart!
And just what the hell is
that supposed to mean?!
[KONDO]
Yeah, you've gotten stronger,
and everybody knows it!
But that's not the only thing
that makes a good leader,
you've gotta be more
than a tough guy!
[MISAKI]
We finally made it!
[SHIROKAWA] Whoaa, what
a blast from the past!
[KUROSAKI] Yayyy!
Shirokawa?
[SHIROKAWA]
The sofa and table
are still here!
[KUROSAKI]
Whoa, but it's dirty!
Y'all should clean up a bit!
[SHIROKAWA]
You're the only one here?
Where're the other guys at?
You have some guts
to say that to me.
[SHIROKAWA]
This place sure has
gotten lonely, huh? (smack)
Hey, no fighting! Agh!
[USUI]
That's enough, Miss President.
[MISAKI]
Usui! Hey! Let me go!
[KUROSAKI] It's all right, Misa.
For the guys here sometimes...
this is the only way they can
say what they wanna say.
This is how they communicate.
[KUROSAKI]
It might look like they're just
fighting with each other,
but to them it's actually
a conversation.
[SHIROKAWA]
Looks like I remember some of
the old moves after all.
Even though it's been awhile
since I've had a good fight.
[SHIROKAWA]
Still, it sure was one hell of a
surprise to fight you.
[SHIROKAWA]
When did you suddenly
get so strong?
(chuckle) The hell. Looks
like you're still a big ol'
cry baby though.
[SHIROKAWA]
But you've got resolve.
Heh. You didn't really think
you'd be able to hide those
tears from me, did you, buddy?
You've gotten a lot bigger since
the last time I saw you‐ you're
taller and your hair's longer,
and with that headband I
didn't recognize you at first.
You remember me...
after so long?
[SHIROKAWA]
Of course. (laughing)
How've you been doin,
ya dumbasses?
[ALL]
Sir!
Now do you see?
Yeah...
I can't believe
how easily
you fall in line
for this guy.
He's just an idiot
with a lame nickname.
Kurotatsu, quit
being mean!
When I was a first year,
I was so weak...
It made me want to be
strong no matter what.
I took on a group of guys I
didn't stand a chance against,
and just as they were beating
the crap out of me...
A hero came and
saved me from them.
[SHIROKAWA] Hey, get
over here, bastard!
[ARATAKE] And I...
I wanted to be a hero,
too! Just like you!
[SHIROKAWA] You will. Trust me.
[ARATAKE] (crying)
[KUROSAKI]
Shiroyan, don't tell
me you're gonna‐
[SHIROKAWA]
Nah, don't worry about that.
I'm not that idiot who
makes his mom cry anymore.
Plus, we've got our
own stuff to... huh?
[SARASHINA] Sob.
[SHIROKAWA] Ah, there he is!
Whatcha doin', Ikkun?
[SARASHINA]
Nothing. Nothing at all.
What's up? Are you
mad at us, Ikkun?
Forget it. You don't have
to worry about me anymore.
What're you saying, dummy?
Don't tell me you forgot
about our important mission?
[SARASHINA] Mission?
[SHIROKAWA] Our special speed
training
to get our photo taken
with Misa, remember?!
[SARASHINA]
Why don't you just go do it with
your other friends?
That bandana guy can
take my place and‐
[SHIROKAWA] You dummy!
Ahhhh!
If we don't have you, Ikkun,
there's no way we'll win!
But why? You can at least
play poker, can't you?!
[SHIROKAWA]
C'mon, quit arguing about it!
THIS stuff suits me way
more than the old way did.
Wh‐who are all of you?
[ARATAKE]
Are you Shirokawa's
new followers?
[TAHARA]
Where'd you go to junior high?
[KONDO] Are you strong?
[AOI] Wait a second...
Why does it seem like things
are getting dangerous?
[USUI]
It's not like they're
picking a fight or anything.
[ARATAKE]
So then Shirokawa's the number
one guy there, too?
[TAHARA]
Has he gotten in any fights?
[USUI]
I guess we can't mention how you
ripped out
Shirokawa's earrings
with your bare hands, huh?
[MISAKI] Gah!
[ARATAKE] Woman,
what did you do?!
[SHIROKAWA]
Hey, you guys,
what're you doing?
[SARASHINA]
That girl isn't just
some punk leader!
[KUROSAKI] That's right! She's
our boss, our goddess! Our maid
and president!
[MISAKI] Ah!
[ARATAKE] A maid?
Yes! All who resist her will
be sent to the abyss!
She's earned the nickname
"Misaki from Hell"...
and she is none other than
our student council president!
Got it? So you guys better
show her some more respect!
[KUROSAKI] Bow your heads!
[ALL]
Our apologies, Miss President!
Cut that out,
you three idiots!
[TRIO]
She's mad, she's mad! Nice!
(ARATAKE laughing)
(laughter)
Wait a sec... aren't we
forgetting something?
[ALL] Huh?
[YUKIMURA]
(sniffle) I sure am hungry...
[USUI]
Today, we got to see a
different side to the
Three Idiots. Okay, done.
[SHIROKAWA]
Whoa, talk about
brushing us aside!
[KUROSAKI]
I wouldn't want any of Usui's
compliments anyway. Right,
Shiroyan?
[SARASHINA]
What did you think, Misa?
[MISAKI]
Huh? I didn't really care.
[TRIO] Huh?
[SARASHINA] Maybe next time I,
Ikkun, will get a backstory!
[MISAKI] The Three Idiots
aren't even in the next episode,
are they?
[TRIO] Huh?!
[MISAKI]
I should know all of Seika's
students, but who's this
suspicious guy wearing a hoodie?
[USUI]
You should be more
careful, Ayuzawa.
[YUKIMURA]
Miss President!
I got free and now I'm back!
[MISAKI]
Oh, sorry, Yukimura.
We forgot about you.