(laughing merrily)
[MISAKI] Listen to
THIS, Yukimura!
[YUKIMURA] Huh?
Just now, I heard some junior
high‐school students talking in
front of our school, and...
[GIRL A]
Seika High School sure
has changed a lot, huh?
[GIRL B]
Yeah... It's not so scary
anymore. Like it actually
seems kinda nice.
(MISAKI welling with excitement)
[MISAKI]
And that's what they said!
[YUKIMURA]
Wow! It looks like all of our
hard work is finally starting
to pay off!
[MISAKI]
With the way things are going
more and more female students
will enroll, I'm sure of it.
I'm thankful we had such
great members on the student
council this semester.
Next week we have an open campus
for junior high students who are
about to move into high school.
If we keep up the good work,
Seika's female population is
going to skyrocket!
[YUKIMURA]
Hm... There sure are a lot
of notes from the girls in
the opinion box.
[MISAKI]
And stupid drawings
from the guys.
Even though things are much
better, there's still plenty
left to do.
Okay! First, let's decide
who will address each matter
on the table,
then proceed in order
of most important to‐ Uh?
President.
Lend me a towel or a hair dryer.
(MISAKI annoyed)
What do you think you're doing?
[YUKIMURA]
UH, um, if you need a towel...
and if you don't mind using
mine, I can give you this one.
(tiptoeing closer)
I was going to use
it for P.E. today...
but I ended up not
using it at all.
What are you,
a girl in love?!
He's acting all nervous
around me. What for?
Because you're an
equal‐opportunity
sexual harasser!
[MISAKI] Open your eyes,
you pervert!
[YUKIMURA] M‐my first kiss...
Well? What happened to you?
You look like a drowned rat.
About that...
[BOY A]
Damn! It won't turn!
[BOY B]
Geez, and you're always
bragging how strong you are.
[BOY A]
Shut up! This thing is
WAY too friggin' tight!
[BOY C]
How're we gonna
turn on the water?
Usui, over heeere!
[BOY B]
Yeah, Usui'll definitely
be able to do something!
There.
(BOYS shocked)
That's why.
Are you an idiot?!
You should've said that first!
I'll go take a look right away.
I shall accompany him.
Usui! You go, too!
Well, Yukimura,
thanks for letting me
borrow your towel.
[USUI]
I'll make sure to use it on
every single part of my body.
Like there, and there,
and even under there.
Yukimura, that look on your face
is starting to weird me out.
Could you quit
blushing like that?
All right then, moving
on to the next item.
Let's take a look at the
budget for next week's
open campus‐ What's wrong?
Well it's just I can't
seem to find the treasury
notebook anywhere...
You lost it?
But I had it right here
just a minute ago, I swear!
Hey, has anyone seen his
notebook lying... around...?
(KOSUGI snoring) (smack)
Dammit, Secretary!
You've got some nerve dozing off
during our meeting like this!
O‐oh... Sorry, Pres, but...
I'm just so tired that I
can't help it... (snoring)
[MISAKI]
Pull yourself together!
[ARAMAKI] Miss President,
calm down! Please!
[KANOU] Hmph.
[MISAKI]
He's not even writing down any
of the meeting minutes! Aaargh!
(morning chatter and laughter)
Good morning.
[TRIO] Good morning to you,
Miss President.
[MISAKI, thinking]
I'm warning people about their
[MISAKI, thinking] Things are
going great!
[KATATA]
My apologies, Miss President.
Oh, hey there, Katata.
You're always so punctual,
it's weird that you're la‐
What the heck is thaaaaat?!
Is something the
matter, ma'am?
(school bell rings)
[KATATA]
Well, e‐excuse my attire,
I don't know what came over me.
Dude, are you sure
you're feeling okay?
(MISAKI sighs)
[SAWA] President, I'm sorry.
I've looked all over, but
I can't find the treasury
notebook anywhere.
[MISAKI] Here.
[SAWA] AH!
I filled in as much as
I could from memory.
It won't be entirely accurate,
but we can use that until we
find the original.
You filled in the whole
thing just from memory?!
You even recorded the figures
from yesterday's meeting!
That's because thanks
to a certain slacker
our minutes from yesterday
were completely useless.
Hey, Hayase. Isn't this
is the list of nurse's
office attendees?
Should this be in the trash?
Huh? It shouldn't be.
How the heck did this
get in there...?
(thinking) Strange. This is
a mistake an organized guy
like him would never make.
Then there was Katata this
morning and Kosugi yesterday...
Just what is going on?
(giggling)
No way!
So then‐
[GIRL A]
Huh? That guys' wearing
a hoodie again.
[GIRL B]
He's even got his hood
up. Isn't he hot?
(GIRLS confused)
[KANOU]
You're on the student
council, aren't you?
Uh? Yeah, can I help you?
(soft guitar music playing
over broadcast system)
Huh? What's that?
[YUKIMURA]
Maybe it's a test broadcast.
Doesn't that music seem
kind of off to you?
[MISAKI]
It's kinda making
me feel sleepy.
(bite)
Hey, just what is
going on in here?
Huh?!
Who are you? Are you
on the committee?
Why's your face covered‐ you
have a cold or something?
Uh, yeah! (fake coughing)
[MISAKI] Is this supposed to be
a test broadcast or something?
[KANOU] Um, y‐yeah.
Can't you change the music
to something else? This
song's putting me to sleep.
[KANOU] That's the point. It
relaxes you, putting you into
a state of intoxication...
(door closing)
UH? What?
[KANOU]
This makes it easy to
influence even smart
individuals like yourself.
[KANOU]
Once your guard is down, you
make a rather willing subject.
Taking the words of
others so seriously...
True, you are the heart
of the student council.
And I will have you make a
disgrace of yourself not only in
front of all of the faculty,
but in front of the
entire school as well.
Seika doesn't need any
more female students.
(waking up groan)
You awake, President?
You were passed out in the
broadcasting room,
so I brought you to
the nurse's office.
What were you doing
sleeping in there?
What'syer problem? (hiccup)
Whazzis? It's jusht you, Usui.
Whatcha doin' in here?
I got it. Come t'plant another
smoochie‐smooch on ol' Yukimura,
izzat it? Ya big friggin'
pervert! (laughter)
(chuckles awkwardly)
[MISAKI] Usui, ya idjit!
[USUI] President, did you happen
to drink something strange?
[MISAKI] You friggin' sekshally
harass too friggin' much!
[USUI] No use talking
to her, huh?
It doesn't seem like you've
had any alcohol, Misa.
Okay. Ow...
(happy) Thisis a lot sofer
than I thought it'd be!
I thought it'd more
prickly or somethin'.
(laughing) Thisiss fuuun!
Okay, okay. Stop.
[TEACHER]
There's no "drunken student"
here at all.
[TEACHER]
Are you sure that's
what you saw?
It would appear that
I was mistaken.
My apologies for the bother.
What'cha doin' withat?
(drunken groan)
Once you snap out of
this, you'll never
believe what happened.
I want to make sure I have
plenty of proof to show you.
Okay, President,
it's interview time!
[USUI] You feeling good?
[MISAKI] I'm feelin' good!
[USUI] You having fun?
[MISAKI] I'm havin' fun!
[USUI] You drunk?
[MISAKI] I'm drunk!
President try not to get
too angry with me, okay?
Who're you talkin' to?
To the future you when
you see these pictures.
Now then, how are we...?
Hold on! What are you taking
your clothes off for?
Hmnh... Cuz I'm way
too hot right now!
Miss President...
Are you trying to seduce me?
[MISAKI]
U‐argh! What're you doin'?!
[USUI]
Oh, my. Where'd this
rope come from?
[MISAKI]
Usui! (struggling) It's hot!
[Usui]
Nice. You look
like a spring roll.
It's hot!
Wasn't that fun, Misa?
(MISAKI groaning)
Please I'm begging you...
You have to let me go...
Oh please, my Master.
Didja think I'd say that,
ya pervert bastard?!
Wow.
I'm so hot...
Take my clothes off Usui.
You really need to be
more careful what you
say around me, Ayuzawa.
It's hot. Usui...
Hurry up and‐
Not a chance.
You big meanie.
It's time for you
to rest now, okay?
[SAKURA] Shizuko!
[SHIZUKO] Yes?
[SAKURA] Wanna walk
home together?
Very well,
shall we go?
[SAKURA] It sure was hot today!
[SHIZUKO] It was indeed.
[SAKURA]
Hot ramen is good on
a day like this, huh?
[SHIZUKO]
If you say so...
Oh, look. An earthworm.
(SAKURA squealing)
Have you noticed that
something's kinda "off"
about the Pres today?
Yeah, she's been that
way since this morning.
(thinking) It's a dream...
(from phone)
[USUI] You drunk?
[MISAKI] I'm drunk!
[MISAKI, thinking]
More like a nightmare!
I can't believe that happened!
So, President, did you
bump into anyone in the
broadcasting room?
The broadcasting room?
That's where I found
you sleeping, Misa.
Yeah, that's right...
I went to the broadcasting room
and ran into that weird guy.
But is something like that...
really possible?
In that case it looks like you
were probably hypnotized by
someone...
Someone with a grudge against
you, someone who really wanted
you to humiliate yourself.
It can't be!
[YUKIMURA]
Wait! Mr. Usui,
what are you doing?
[USUI]
Don't worry about it.
Okay, there he is.
E‐excuse me, I'm sorry!
Mr. Usui!
Thanks for your
help, Yukimura.
[USUI] Thanks for
dressing like a girl.
(YUKIMURA crying)
That's a man?
So you really hate
girls that much, huh...
Soutarou Kanou...
of Class... 1‐7.
(shocked)
[USUI]
It seems like you have
a very interesting skill.
(breath) Do you want to
see? I'll do it extra
special for you.
Look deep into my eyes.
What happened? Is this
your true self, Yukimura?
No!
[KANOU]
Look deep into my eyes.
Usui Takumi... From now on you
will hate Misaki Ayuzawa.
(snapping fingers)
Hmph.
Yeah, right.
(KANOU shocked)
Just who exactly do you think
you're dealing with, Kanou?
Is Soutarou Kanou in here?!
Uh?!
Looks like I finally found you.
Miss Ayuzawa just stepped
out a little while ago.
She was looking through
this years' class photos
when she suddenly yelled,
"That's him!" and ran out.
[MISAKI]
I heard a rumor, Kanou...
Apparently, you have
something against girls.
Guess that explains why you
tried to set me up like that.
If I wasn't student council
president, we wouldn't have
more girl students.
That's what you thought, right?
Sorry to disappoint you
but all the girls and I
are here to stay!
Whether you like it or not!
Because I believe that is the
path Seika must take to become
a better school.
But if you have an opinion
on this, I'd like to hear it.
I will work to accommodate your
needs to the best of my ability.
Because that's my duty as
student council president.
Very well.
Huh‐ what the? HUH? Why
can't I remember what we
were just talking about?
President, though it's
strange for me to say it,
you'd do well to realize
you're very open to
hypnotic suggestion.
Too bad, Usui. Your beloved
student council president is
going to absolutely hate you.
[KANOU]
In the next 24 hours, from
now till 5 PM tomorrow, if
she sleeps even a wink...
when the President awakens,
she will hate you more than
anything else in the world.
Looks like the "unbeatable
duo" is done for.
[USUI]
Stupid! Stupid! Careless,
clueless and air‐headed Misa
is a big fat stupidhead!
Okay, shut up
already, I get it!
Oh my, Usui! I see
you're using a different
approach today!
No one asked you to work today,
did they? Just get out!
But how can I possibly
stand to be apart from
you at a time like this?
There's no way I'm
letting you sleep tonight.
Quit saying things that'll
give people the wrong idea!
[SATSUKI] Oh! How romantic!
[MISAKI]
See you tomorrow, guys.
What do you think
you're doing, Usui?
You've worked so hard,
Misa. It's finally over.
Just let me change
so I can go home.
I'll help you change‐
Get out.
[MISAKI]
Usui, how far do you
plan on following me?
[USUI]
All the way.
[MISAKI]
In case you haven't noticed,
you're being even
creepier than usual.
That damn Kanou, what
exactly was the point of
hypnotizing me like that?
He wants me to hate you...
[MISAKI]
But I ALREADY hate you, so I
just don't get it at all. (sigh)
[USUI]
Heh. It probably didn't look
that way to Kanou.
Whatever. That guy needs
to get his eyes checked.
[MISAKI]
I'll ask you one more
time, Usui: how far do
you plan on following me?
I told you, all the way!
One moment please,
I'm calling the police.
Huh? You meanie.
Haven't you had enough?
Go home already!
What happened today was due
to my own carelessness.
I'm going to spend the
night reflecting on that.
Now leave me alone!
(smile) True to form...
[MISAKI]
I'm done in the bath
if you wanna go.
Your phone's been ringing
for a while now, Sis‐
hurry up and answer it.
(cell ringing)
That's unusual.
I wonder who it is?
Maybe it's someone calling to
tell us that one of the entries
I submitted in your name
has won something.
(click) Hello‐ who is this?
[USUI]
Hey, it's me. Me, y'know, ME.
(angry)
What'd they say? Did they
tell us we won something good?
Well, I guess I'll review for
tomorrow's classes.
(cell ringing)
[USUI]
It's me.
[MISAKI]
If this is a prank caller,
you've made your point.
Me. How cruel, Misa. You know
who this is, don't you?
How the heck did you
even get this number?
[USUI] Love makes all‐
[MISAKI] I'm hanging up.
(cell ringing)
[MISAKI]
(sigh)(click) Do you know how
many times you've called?
[USUI]
Uh, around 20 maybe?
[MISAKI]
This is the 22nd time,
you stalker!
I can't focus on my work!
[USUI]
I figured if you did
nothing but study, you'd
start to feel tired.
I'm used to pulling all
nighters, so studying without
rest is no problem for me.
And like I said, I already hate
you so you can quit with the‐‐
[USUI]
You love me.
[USUI] Ayuzawa... you love me.
[MISAKI] Uh...
(hang up)
What's his problem?!
Is he an idiot?!
You hate me... huh?
Who'd fall in love
with someone like that?
Besides, I'm not
doing this for him.
I just don't want to lose to
that manipulative jerk Kanou.
[USUI]
Good morning, Miss President!
The news says it'll rain around
noon today. How about we share
an umbrella?
Usui...
Don't just casually read
someone else's newspaper!
But I got bored
waiting for you.
Wait‐ were you out
here all night?!
[SUZUNA]
Sis, breakfast is ready.
Quick, look at today's
comic strip is really funny!
[SUZANA]
Oh, in this one it looks like
he has a long lost brother...
[MISAKI]
Come on, let's go eat breakfast.
You haven't eaten, right?
Next time, I really
will call the police.
A pastry...? (amused)
This is past the
expiration date.
[MISAKI]
If you got a problem
with that, don't eat it!
Wow, it's really
coming down huh?
This sucks, my
vision's all blurry.
Guess that's what I get for
staying up all last night.
If you're feeling sleepy
I can give you a supplement
that'll help.
A supplement?
It's blueberry extract,
it works pretty well!
I always make sure to
have a little on hand.
Oh, no! I left it
in the classroom!
So much for keeping them "on
hand". Hurry and go get 'em.
Yes, ma'am!
Yukimura's kind of a
health nut, isn't sh‐ HE?
Yeah. Looks like it.
[USUI]
Well? Are you sure you're
not feeling sleepy?
[MISAKI]
Quit bugging me!
I told you I'd be fine.
[YUKIMURA]
Thank goodness! I found it!
[KANOU]
Excuse me...
Yes? What is it?
Huh? What are you
swallowing it whole for,
I thought you were
supposed to chew them?
They're like blueberry
candies aren't they?
Wait‐ really?!
Let me see the package real
quick, Yukimura.
Oh, this is it.
Oh sure. Yukimura, what does
this look like to you?
My blueberry
supplements.
[USUI]
When you went to get
this, there was guy
with a hood and glasses
hanging around, right?
[YUKIMURA]
Huh? Yeah, how did you know?
Don't tell me!
President, do you
think you can guess
what side effects this
pain reliever has?
Kanou! I'll get you!
[USUI]
Less than one hour to go.
[MISAKI]
Dammit! I'm so
freakin' tired‐ ugh!
You're normally not the type
to take medicine at all, are
you, Miss President?
Of course not!
Medicine is expensive!
What a waste of money,
I can get better on my
own! (dead)
[USUI]
Please quit shaking like that.
[MISAKI]
I can't focus in here!
I'm going to get some fresh air.
[MISAKI]
Usui. I've got a favor to ask.
Will you please hit me?
If you hit me, I think the sheer
force of my anger and rage
will blow away all
of this sleepiness.
In return, you have to let me
get a swing in, too.
It'll wake me up.
The lack of sleep is really
starting to get to you isn't it,
President?
Besides, there's no
way I'd ever hurt you.
[USUI]
You're always jumping
into things, alone.
Like yesterday. You could've
waited for me instead of
confronting Kanou alone.
And just why should I have to
wait for you... oh... if I'm
going to talk to Kanou?
The thing about hypnosis is...
if the listener feels even the
slightest bit of doubt,
the hypnotic suggestion
won't be effective.
That's why he can't have
any control over me.
Miss President, I...
You're the one person
I'd never want to hate me.
(laugh) There you go again.
You're always making fun of me.
You really piss me off...
you know that?
But, I'm...
I'm so grateful to you...
I wonder if I'll...
forget about that, too.
Gratitude for the
sports festival...
for Miyabigaoka, and
for the school festival...
I still haven't repaid you...
for everything...
for all the things
you've done for me...
[USUI]
That's fine. Even if you never
repay me, I'll help you whenever
you need.
And I will make you fall in love
with me, over and over again.
Just leave it to your "Master."
N‐now you're just...
talking stupid... Dummy...
[KANOU]
23 hours, 55 minutes.
Just five minutes were left to
go. But it would appear that
I am the victor.
[YUKIMURA]
Uh, where did Miss
President go? Uh, Vice
President Yukimura here!
[KATATA]
Discipline Committee President
Katata here. Please forgive my
behavior earlier.
[SAWA]
And I'm Sawa, who lost
the treasury notebook.
[KOSUGI]
I'm Bunta Kosugi, the guy
who was dozing off.
[ARAMAKI]
I'm Aramaki, president of
the P.E. Committee.
[UTSUMI]
I'm Utsumi, who lives in
constant fear of our Student
Council President...
[HAGIMOTO]
I'm Hagimoto, who did the
awesome narration for the
sports festival!
[HAYASE]
I'm Hayase, the mostly silent
president of the School Health
Committee.
[YUKIMURA]
Let's all work together to make
this the best open campus ever!
[STUDENT COUNCIL]
Yeah!