Honoka, you look
so cute in that dress.
[HONOKA] Thank you‐
and you too, Subaru.
[MISAKI] My apologies for the
wait. Here you are, Masters.
[MISAKI] If you'll excuse me.
[CUSTOMERS] Okay...
[SATSUKI] Oh, hey Misa, can I
borrow that tray for a second?
[MISAKI] Wait, don't‐!
[SATSUKI] That's not
one of our trays!
Sorry about that. I made it to
help with resistance training.
[SATSUKI] Wh‐What's that thing
even made of?
I‐It... The floor! It went
through the floor!
[MISAKI] It's just a piece of
scrap metal I found.
The size is perfect, huh?
[SATSUKI] What a
terrifying utensil!
[USUI] Miss President, are you
doing that because the sports
[MISAKI] Of course I am.
I will get first place
in all categories
and collect trophies left and
right!
For the sake of the women of
Seika High, I will succeed!
[ARAMAKI] And on that note...
[ARAMAKI] the 81st Seika High
School
Sports Festival is now underway!
Everyone do your best!
[YUKIMURA] Pretty worked up,
aren't they?
[KOSUGI] It's to be expected,
Yukimura.
Seika High's sports festival
is a battle between all the
classes
but there are only enough girls
for one female team.
[KOSUGI] And this year, there's
been a change
to the rules that's raised the
stakes even higher...
For the first time, each event
has an award!
These prizes go to the team
whose member gets first place.
On top of that, this morning's
main event, the obstacle course,
has a very special prize...
[SAKURA] NOOOOO! I DON'T WANNA!
[GOUDA] It's too late for that!
It was decided in a school‐wide
survey
and the numbers don't lie!
You're the girl
we want a kiss from!
[SAKURA] No! No way!
[MISAKI] I'm sorry, this is all
my fault! I meant to get rid of
that reward before the festival,
but I completely forgot!
[MISAKI] But it's too late to
turn back now,
the whole school
knows about it...
[GOUDA] A KISS from Sakura
Hanazono's lips!
I, Gouda, will do whatever it
takes to steal it!
[SAKURA] Misaki...
Please... Please
don't make me kiss that weirdo!
[MISAKI] Don't worry... I
promise, I won't let that
happen!
Because if anyone comes anywhere
near you, I will...
Eliminate them!
[GOUDA] R‐Retreat!
Don't think I'll be defeated
that easily!
[UTSUMI] It looks like things
are even more heated this year,
huh?
[YUKIMURA] Actually, I was
absent last year...
This'll be the first sports
festival I've gone to.
I'm actually really excited
about it!
[SUDO] Usui!
Why won't you run for us in the
1,000‐meter dash?
You're our fastest guy!
[SUDO] The prize is 30 extra
large cutlet curries!
That's three whole months‐worth
of food!
[USUI] I'm not racing.
[GONDA] He said the same
thing last year too, didn't he?
[SUDO] Let's just give up.
Maybe we have a chance of
winning it on our own...
[HAGIMOTO] And the Seika Sports
Festival has at last kicked off!
Live coverage will be
brought to you courtesy of me,
Hagimoto of the Broadcasting
Club.
Which class will be the victor,
and does the girls' team
stand a chance?
First up, as always, is the
100‐meter dash.
It looks like the competition
is going to be fierce!
Student Council President
Ayuzawa of the girls' team
already exudes an aura of
incredible determination!
[GIRLS] Go, Misaki! Do your
best!
[HAGIMOTO] The competition is
about to start!
The prize at stake is one
month's worth of your favorite
songs
broadcasted over the
morning announcements!
I'm gonna take first
and blast nothin' but
hardcore death metal
with extreme guitar riffs!
[HAGIMOTO] Uh oh,
what's happened to Class 2‐6?
Looks like he's frozen up at the
starting line!
Sure enough, President Ayuzawa
is already taking the lead‐ Huh?
[KOSUGI] A demon...
[ARAMAKI] I'm scared!
[HAGIMOTO] Goaaaal!
[GIRL] So cool!
[SAKURA] Misaki, you're so cool!
[GIRL] Ayuzawa is incredible!
Thanks to her we'll be able to
sit back and relax for once!
[GUY] I figured something like
this would happen...
She's already kicking our butts
and the festival just started...
Not to worry‐ there are still
plenty of prizes remaining.
[HAGIMOTO] First place in the
200‐meter dash goes to the
girls' team!
[GUYS] Not again!
[HAGIMOTO] First place in the
400‐meter dash goes to the
girls' team!
[MISAKI] Victory!
[HAGIMOTO] First place in the
1,500‐meter dash
[HAGIMOTO]
GOES TO THE GIRLS' TEAM!
[GUY] You think we're gonna
stand for this?!
She can't just go out every
single time!
[ARAMAKI] Um, but there's
no rule saying
she CAN'T compete
in every event.
[GUY] So what! This isn't fair
to us‐ we suck!
[MISAKI] "Unfair"? Are you
freaking kidding me?
I've been...
fighting with everything
I've got!
[SAKURA] Misaki, are you all
right?
[SHIZUKO] Here. It's oxygen.
[HAGIMOTO] Will participants
in the chicken fight
please assemble.
[SHIZUKO] The next event is the
chicken fight.
[SAKURA] Misaki, you should try
and get some rest!
[MISAKI] Damn...
I thought I'd be able to compete
in everything by myself.
[SAKURA] You don't have to do
that, Misaki!
[SHIZUKO] After all, the girls'
team has a handicap.
Even if we don't compete,
we'll still get points.
[MISAKI] We may get points, but
we won't get the first‐place
prize, will we?
I want to get as many of those
prizes as I possibly can.
I want the sports festival to be
something the girls can actually
enjoy for once!
[SAKURA] Misakiii!
Ahh, Sakura!
It's time to take... a tiny
break.
[MISAKI] All right.
[HAGIMOTO] Okay, next up
is the 1,000‐meter dash!
[MISAKI] I sat out the chicken
fight, so I HAVE to do my best
on this one.
[GUY] She did it! She won again!
[HAGIMOTO] First place
in the 1,000‐meter dash
[GUY] Get outta here you demon!
[HAGIMOTO] goes to
the girls team!
[GUY] Gouda... are you sure we
have a shot at getting' first
place?
[GOUDA] Hmph.
If push comes to shove,
I'll do whatever it takes
to win.
[HAGIMOTO] And now, the final
morning event, the obstacle
course, is about to begin.
It's a competition with no
limits for entry!
Who will be the one to race
across the school grounds,
clearing obstacles left and
right to claim victory, and take
first place!
[HAGIMOTO] And who will be the
one to win that coveted kiss?!
[MISAKI] I will protect Sakura!
[GUY] Th‐this is bad...
She's already out for blood
and the competition
hasn't even started yet!
You really wanna go up against
her, Gouda?
[GOUDA] Of course, like I said:
I'll do whatever it takes.
[ARAMAKI] Take your positions.
And...
[HAGIMOTO] They've all come
flying out at once!
First up is...
that old standby, the slope!
Oh, dear! Several contestants
have already been disqualified!
Next up is‐ the tight rope!
Anyone with a fear of heights,
it's curtains for you!
Several contestants are already
out, and the top contenders
are...
Gouda of Class 3‐2
and Miss Ayuzawa of Class 2‐1!
The two of them
have just entered the pool area!
Falling into the water at any
point will mean instant
disqualification!
[MISAKI] Dammit! I'm starting to
run out of strength.
But... No matter what,
I have to protect Sakura!
I'm... gonna... fall!
What the?!
[GOUDA] Usui? Why?!
[HAGIMOTO] Oh, my! With this,
Gouda takes a commanding lead!
[MISAKI] Dammit! I have to catch
up to‐
[USUI] Although I like it when
you give it your all, I think
it's safe to say...
Just leave this to me.
[MISAKI] He's so fast!
I have to hurry and catch up to
them!
[HAGIMOTO] And up next is the
volleyball court!
Gouda is all alone
and in first place!
[GOUDA] Yes! At this rate,
Sakura Hanazono's lips
are all mine!
[USUI] That was a pretty cheap
trick you pulled back there, Mr.
Gouda.
[HAGIMOTO] WHOA! What a surprise
this is!
Takumi Usui has tied for the top
spot!
And President Ayuzawa
is quickly gaining on them!
On top of that,
the Volleyball Club has launched
its attack!
[HAGIMOTO] The top two
contenders
have entered the
school grounds.
The goal is in sight!
[GOUDA] Crap!
Trip, dammit!
[USUI] Too bad. Looks like you
missed.
[HAGIMOTO] Goaaaal! First place
goes to Takumi Usui of Class
2‐2!
[MISAKI] Excuse me...
[HAGIMOTO] And in second place
is President Ayuzawa!
And so, as our first place
winner, Takumi Usui will now...
receive his victory kiss
from Sakura Hanazono!!
[MISAKI] I'm sorry, Sakura.
[SAKURA] It's all right, Misaki.
I know you did your best!
[USUI] What's this? The prize is
to "RECEIVE" a kiss?
Then, I'll pass.
[MISAKI]
[USUI] I'm not the type that
likes BEING kissed...
I'm more about doing the kissing
myself.
[HAGIMOTO] Uh‐ and so, the kiss
goes to our next runner up...
President Ayuzawa!
[SAKURA] Smooch!
[GOUDA] If I'd just kept going I
would've gotten second place...!
[SHIZUKO] That was awfully
lucky.
[SAKURA] Yeah.
[ALL] Finished!
[KUROSAKI] Isn't it perfect?!
[SHIROKAWA] Great work,
Kurotatsu!
[SARASHINA] I think I might cry!
[HAGIMOTO] Now then, we'll be
breaking for lunch
before the
afternoon events!
[SUZUNA] Sis, you sure
have been busy, haven't you?
Class got out early today,
so I came to watch you.
[MISAKI] Suzuna!
[SUZUNA] I've learned that
postcard giveaways
aren't the
only way to win prizes.
Next week the neighborhood
committee is also having a
sports festival,
and two weeks from now is the
shopping mall's sports festival.
[SUZUNA] Enter those, okay?
[KUROSAKI] I ditch the sports
fest
And sew up this dress
Am I not the best?
[SHIROKAWA] Kurotatsu, good job!
[SARASHINA] You're so talented
that it's creepy!
[KUROSAKI] So, when do you think
we should we give Misa her
special present?
[SHIROKAWA] She's gonna love
it...
[SARASHINA] Hey, someone's
coming! Hurry up and hide that!
[KUROSAKI] But where?!
[SHIROKAWA] Over here‐
stick it in one of these
bags full of clothes!
[KUROSAKI] Here‐ put it in there
before someone sees!
[HAGIMOTO] And now, we will
begin the afternoon events!
[MISAKI] I was so hellbent on
not participating in this that I
forgot all about it...
[USUI] Hey, President, are you
doing this event, too?
[MISAKI] Actually, I think I'm
gonna go ahead and pass on this
one...
[USUI] But why?
Pretty ironic, huh?
The costume race almost seems
like it was MADE just for you.
[USUI] It's all right. It's
not like wearing a silly costume
is going to give away your
secret part‐time job.
Let's cosplay!
[MISAKI] You wanna get slapped?
[USUI] If you do it, I'll do it,
too.
[MISAKI] Just go by yourself!
[SHIZUKO] Misaki! Please leave
the costume race to me!
[SHIZUKO] Each team must have at
least one member compete in this
as well.
[SHIZUKO] But asking you to
enter every single event is far
too unreasonable.
I couldn't do that in good
conscience.
[SAKURA] I'll be doing it, too,
so just rest, okay?
[SHIZUKO] Also, this event seems
to be a magnet for others such
as myself,
[SHIZUKO] who are not athletic
in the slightest.
Therefore I feel that I MUST
contribute!
[SAKURA] Oh! But don't you have
to change clothes in front of
everyone?
[SHIZUKO] Indeed‐ but fear not.
I have prepared this poncho
exactly for that purpose.
[SAKURA] Wow, Shizuko, it's like
you've been planning this all
along!
[SHIZUKO] With this‐
there's nothing to worry about.
[MISAKI] That's not true,
Shizuko!
[MISAKI] I couldn't live with
myself...
[MISAKI] if I sent some
defenseless girl into the midst
of a pack of wolves, butt naked!
Therefore....
I will compete in this event!
[HAGIMOTO] Continuing on,
will the participants for the
12th event,
the costume race, please
assemble at the starting line.
[MISAKI] It's okay, it's okay!
No one will know I'm a maid.
[USUI] President. You're moving
your arms and legs in tandem it
looks weird.
Are you sure you're okay
with being the only girl
in the entire event?
No one else wanted to do it.
[MISAKI] I'll be fine, thanks.
Okay... go for a costume that
doesn't stand out and head
straight for the goal.
[GUY] Aw man, it's about to
start.
Just having to watch this stupid
thing is painful.
The participants have absolutely
zero motivation, the costumes
are crap,
and the reward is even crappier.
The principal's "lucky, academic
ability‐increasing pencil"?
[GUY] Who the hell would want
that thing?
[YUKIMURA] Oh, Miss President!
Are you competing for the girls'
team again?
[MISAKI] Yukimura!
[YUKIMURA] Huh? Mr. Usui, you're
competing too?
But isn't this event mainly
for the weaker competitors who
aren't very good at sports?
[USUI] Yeah, I'm just doing it
because the President's in it
too.
[MISAKI] Are you not the
athletic type, Yukimura?
[YUKIMURA] Yeah, I'm awful.
When it comes to sports all I do
is drag the rest
of the team down...
[YUKIMURA] But here at Seika,
they have an event
that even people like me can
participate in,
and that makes me really happy!
I had to miss out on last year's
festival because I had a cold.
So this year will be
my first time to participate.
[MISAKI] I see...
I'm sure you'll do your best!
[YUKIMURA] Right!
[USUI] I'm sure you'll do YOUR
best, too, won't you, Miss
Cosplay?
[HAGIMOTO] Now then, before we
begin allow me to explain the
rules:
A "costume selection zone" has
been prepared 50 meters from the
starting point.
Please do not take a single look
at the contents when selecting
your bag.
Another 50 meters away
is the changing room.
If you can put your costume on
in the dark
and run one lap around the
track, you win!
The most important point in this
event
is choosing a costume
that is easy to change into!
Now then, all participants,
please assemble at
the starting line!
[GONDA] H‐hey, wait a second,
isn't that...?
Isn't that Usui?!
[SUDO] Why is he competing in
this event
out of all the other ones?!
Well, guess we better
get this over with.
Sure is a pain in the ass
though.
[ARAMAKI] Okay‐ on your mark...!
[MISAKI] They're tired after
only three seconds?!
This is throwing me off!
[USUI] Oh, Miss President.
C'mon, hurry up.
Which one will you choose?
[MISAKI] He's enjoying himself
way too much.
Still, there's no way of knowing
what's inside each bag.
At any rate, choosing one that's
full of lots of clothes is
probably the safest bet.
Now I have to hurry and change
before the tent is crawling with
guys!
[SHIROKAWA] Where could it have
gone?!
[BOTH] Why? Why? Why?
[KUROSAKI] And I put so much
hard work into that costume,
too!
[MISAKI] It's so dark! How the
heck am I even supposed to know
what I'm putting on?
Still, this feels really
familiar somehow...
[USUI] President, what costume
did you get?
[MISAKI] An illusion! That was
some kind of optical illusion
just now!
Yeah, just keep telling yourself
that, President.
But it's definitely a maid
outfit.
[MISAKI] What the hell! Of all
things, why this?!
[USUI] You went for the bag with
the most clothes, didn't you?
Anyway, what's the problem? If
you think about it, it's the
perfect match.
After all, you're a girl.
[MISAKI] Yeah, but that's beside
the point...!
[USUI] Just take a look at those
other guys.
[MISAKI] That's rough!
[USUI] Right?
Now then... will you change
yourself?
Or do I have to do it
by force?
Where do you get off making
a nasty perverted statement
like that, you FREAK?!
[USUI] Uh‐oh.
Yelp!
[MISAKI] What was that dog‐like
noise just now?
[YUKIMURA]
[MISAKI] Yukimura!
[YUKIMURA] That voice is...
Miss President?!
I'm sorry‐ did I
do something wrong?
[MISAKI] Uh no it was an
accident...
[YUKIMURA] I'll leave right now!
[MISAKI] Wait, Yukimura!
[USUI] He's so focused that
he's not even listening.
Still, I think you should be
worrying about yourself instead
of Yukimura.
I almost forgot...
What am I going to do with this?
My outfit's transformed?!
[USUI] That's not it,
President...
[KOSUGI] Who's that in the maid
costume?
[ARAMAKI] Is that Yukimura?!
Is it just me or does he
actually pull that off pretty
well for a guy?
I bet he packed that costume
himself because he wanted to
stand out!
[YUKIMURA] Huh? What're you
saying?
Look at him! He's tryin' to show
off for us, boys!
Oh, is that it?
[YUKIMURA] No! You're wrong!
[STUDENT] He thought he would
add some spice to the event
by dressing up all special!
How KIND of him.
Looks like it worked!
I can't believe those guys!
I'll show them‐!
[USUI] No. You have to change
into a costume before you exit
the tent.
Otherwise, you'll be
disqualified.
[MISAKI] Gaaa! So?! This isn't
the time for that!
[USUI] It can't be helped, can
it?
This is Yukimura's first time
participating,
and with his personality being
the way it is,
he's giving it
his all, but...
The truth is that
out of all of the people
participating in the
event,
no one gives a damn about it.
It's one thing for them to not
be athletic, or good at sports,
but no one will care about an
event where the participants
don't even try.
And even if someone
does make an effort to succeed,
in the end, it's going to be
futile.
[MISAKI] So what you're telling
me is all we can do is sit back
while they point their fingers
and laugh at him for trying?!
[MISAKI] I can't...
I won't allow it!
Doin' all right there, Miss
Maid?
For somethin' you made yourself,
that skirt sure does seem awful
long, doesn't it?
Aww, we didn't hurt his
feelings, did we?
Man that's hilarious!
Huh?
[MISAKI] Are you all right?
Pick yourself up, Yukimura.
Let's finish this together.
Who the hell is that guy?
Hey look, there's someone else!
Usui?!
All of a sudden, those guys took
their costumes to another level!
[USUI] Wait, Miss President.
Did he say "President"?!
What are those two
doing something
like the costume race for?
And they're actually taking it
seriously?!
[MISAKI] So what if we are?
You got a problem with that?
Uh...
No, no problem at all.
For a second I'd started to
convince myself that it was
really cool!
Well, what do you say we race to
the goal,
and cross the finish line while
holding each other's hands‐
[MISAKI] Just shut up and run
so we can get this over with.
[USUI] You know, Miss President,
that costume actually
turned out pretty good on you.
[MISAKI] I said shut up! Just
keep it moving!
[YUKIMURA] U‐uh, guys?
Thank you very much, Miss
President!
[SAKURA] Wow, Misaki! You look
super cool!
[SHIZUKO] I had no idea there
were even costumes like this.
[MISAKI] Uh, actually, we just
threw a bunch of different
things together
and ended up with these.
[ARAMAKI] Miss President,
that's a disqualification.
[MISAKI] Uh, sorry about that...
Still, I thought they ended up
looking pretty good.
[USUI] Truly impressive, Miss
President.
In a single day, you've managed
to cover your entire body in
wounds.
[MISAKI] Say... don't you think
there's a way
to make the costume race better
somehow?
I think we could get the
participants to take things more
seriously
with some improvements.
Maybe if the costumes
were something cooler‐
like super heroes or video game
characters,
people would actually want to
participate...
Maybe I should bring this up
with the student council...
[USUI] Sure. Why not?
[MISAKI] Oh, really?
[USUI] President...
Good work today.
[MISAKI] Don't ever do that
again, you pervert!
[SHIROKAWA] HUHHH?! WHYYYY?!
[KUROSAKI] I spent a whole week
slaving away,
making it just for Misa. All for
nothing...
[MISAKI] Today really wore me
out.
Yo, Usui, you look like
you're free. Do this for me.
C'mon. Do the next episode talk
thing.
[USUI] Oh, it's written right
here. Like this, huuuh?
[YUKIMURA] Mr. Usui, you're not
putting enough into it!
[USUI] Yukimura, looks like
you've got it rough next
episode.
[YUKIMURA] Huh?!
[USUI] And the Three Idiots
appear, too.
[SHIROKAWA] Hey, now!
We won't let you call us
the Three Idiots anymore!
Like they say,
"To know me is to rub me." Yup!
[KUROSAKI] That's not it,
Shiroyan. "To love me is to
grope me." That's it, right?
[SARASHINA] Huh? The title has
"idiots" written in it.
[BOTH] Why?!