[Usui, narrating]
Once upon a time, there lived
an old man and an old woman.
Reckon we'll be havin'
some good weather today!
[Usui, narrating]
One day, Old Woman Sakura
went down to the river
to wash laundry,
and Old Man Yukimura,
rather than going to the
forest to gather firewood,
Huh?
was made to help.
[Usui, narrating]
Just then, a giant peach
came floating down the river.
Wouldja lookie here!
W‐wait up!
Aah! I love me
some peaches!
[Usui, narrating]
The old man and the old woman
carried the peach home...
Glint!
[Usui, narrating]
and prepared to eat it.
(Slice)
Just then...
Ahh! Oh!
[Usui, narrating]
out from the peach, came:
Ta‐daa!
I‐I shall go forward and
slay the demons! Yes, indeed!
Uhh...
D‐Dear, look! A person came
outta that there peach!
Hey, this ain't no time
for face‐stuffin'!
Lately, a band of demons has
been stealing away young maidens
and terrorizing villages
left and right, have they not?
[SAKURA]
Oh, my. The peach done born a
splendid young boy. Munch munch.
I guess it's up to me to
slay these wicked demons!
Yes, indeed!
[SAKURA]
Now now, Momotaro.
It's nothin' you need to be
getting' all worked up over.
O‐oh really?
"Momotaro"?
Dear, you already
thought up a name for him?
I must now go forth
and defeat the demons.
Ooh, aren't you
a handsome one.
Here, reckon you should
take these with you.
We made you
plenty of dumplings,
so be sure to eat up!
Thank you very much,
old woman.
Bye! Take care!
Do yer best, y'hear?!
What was that all about?
Who knows. Let's go eat
some more peach.
[Usui, narrating]
And so, Momotaro set off
to defeat the demons...
[Usui, narrating]
and came upon a dog,
a monkey, and a pheasant.
Why did this happen to us?!
It's your fault, Dog!
You let that guy trick you!
He tricked YOU,
too, Monkey!
It's Pheasant's fault for not
noticing in the first place!
Hey, I'm the one who
said it was suspicious
in the first place!
What are you idiots
doing up there?
Huh? You there! Stranger!
HELP US!
A bad man tricked us and
now he's gonna kill us!
(Sigh)
[Usui, narrating]
The three said that if
Momotaro helped them,
they would do
anything he wished.
[Usui, narrating]
But... they tried to
steal his dumplings,
so he beat the crap out of them.
[Usui]
That's why I tied them up
in the first place.
Ah! It's him!
It's the bad man!
We're gonna die!
Who might you be?
I am Usui.
I'm the leader of the
Three Idiot Circus.
Those are my men.
There's no way
that's true!
Uh... I went to the trouble
of forming a circus,
but those three are
completely useless.
So I was thinking I should
just eat them instead.
I see.
Well, if you're killing
them for food,
I guess that's reasonable.
It's not reasonable at all!
All they ever do is practice,
and because of that,
we're out of food...
You call that "practice"?!
All you do is hit us with a whip
and cackle like you're
having the time of your life!
Now then...
AH!
Who wants to go first?
I'm not tasty at all!
This guy's delicious!
I'm telling you,
THIS guy is!
Yeah, this guy's the
tastiest of us all!
Don't put me in, damnit!
Wait a moment.
You're going to
save us after all?!
I want to ask you one thing
before you get eaten.
You're not gonna
help us at all...
Do you know where the demons
that plague this land live?
We don't know at all...
I see.
Usui, I suggest putting all
three into a nice, hot stew.
I guess I'll be
on my way then.
[THREE IDIOTS]
Ah! Wait, wait, wait!
We don't know where the demons
are, but we know a village
where they were seen recently!
Uh?
It's a village with
a lotta youngsters.
One day the demons
suddenly showed up
and apparently the next
morning all the girls
had up and vanished.
Where might I find
this village?!
We won't tell you
unless you help us.
(Sigh)
Usui...
Very well.
But in exchange...
Give me those dumplings.
[Usui, narrating]
Thus, Momotaro set out,
accompanied by a dog,
a monkey, a pheasant
and the blatantly suspicious
leader of a circus troupe,
to find the demons.
[KUROSAKI]
What about OUR share
of the dumplings?
I ate it all.
NO WAY!
B‐but still,
this is kinda fun, huh?
A party led by a brave warrior,
setting out to defeat
a terrible enemy...
A "party"?
What do you think this is?!
A holiday vacation?!
We're not going on this journey
so you party animals
can have a good time!
[SARASHINA]
Not that kinda "party"!
I mean the five of us together
as a group, with a name!
I suppose a name
would be helpful...
How about...
The Party to Defeat the Demons!
Or "The Demon‐Defeating Party"
for short!
A fine name, is it not?
No objections?
Well then, let us continue!
Is this it...?
So this is where those
poor girls were kidnapped.
The village is
in shambles...
it looks like it's been
completely abandoned.
I'm tellin ya,
that one's all mine!
Tryin' to steal now,
are ya?
That's from my field and
you know it, you damn thief!
NUH‐UH!
This one's from MY field!
Uh, excuse me, sirs...
The hell do you want‐
Got it!
Get back here, you!
Are things like this
because of... the demons?
That stinks!
AH!
Where the heck's he going?!
He said, "it stinks" or
something and suddenly took off.
He is a dog after all‐
his nose is sensitive.
If y'all can't even
handle a smell like that,
then you'd better hurry
and get outta this village
while you still can.
Tell us what happened here!
This village ain't a place
that normal people
can live in no more
it's gotten too bad
for... Ughhhh
Hey! What's wrong?
Are you all‐!
Ah. Looks like he just
couldn't take it anymore...
Somebody please tell us
what's going on!
It's cuz of the women.
When they disappeared
things went downhill fast.
With no one around to take care
of the washin' or cleanin',
things started getting'
really out of hand.
We don't know how to do
any of that crap,
so we've more or less
gone into survival mode.
It's turned into
a total war zone!
Actually, it's kinda
fun not having any
rules to follow.
We can do whatever we want!
Do you really think the women
will be happy when they return
to find that this place has
turned into a total pig‐sty?!
It's not like they're
actually coming back right?
Those guys that
took'em are DEMONS.
We don't stand
a chance.
Right?
I know, right?
Quit screwing around!
We're gonna save your women
whether you like it or not!
Now hurry and tell us
where the demons are, damnit!
Sure is peaceful, huh?
So "Demon Island" is on the
other side of this ocean, huh?
I don't see anything
but the horizon.
Can we really trust
those villagers?
They REALLY didn't
wanna help us!
It's like they didn't
even care if we died!
It seemed like they were
just trying to hurry
and get rid of us.
Let's not go.
Yeah, let's at least
wait another day or two.
We might find some
more reliable info
at a different village.
All right.
Huh?
[MISAKI]
Let's move out!
He just won't listen!
Check out
this turtle!
Let's flip it
on its back!
Ha, ha!
Take that!
Hey! Cut that out!
What're you doing?!
Run away!
He saved that turtle!
Wait, I've heard
about this before!
Heard about what, Monkey?
I heard it from a guy who
heard it from another guy!
If you help a turtle out
it'll reward your kindness by
letting you ride on its shell
to the bottom of the ocean
to party at the Dragon King's
underwater palace.
What's the Dragon King's
palace like?
It's an awesome place
where a sexy princess
gives you all the
fresh seafood you can eat!
Tuna, flounder, crab‐
you name it!
And she gives you a really
special souvenir when you leave!
Really?! Do you think
that turtle will take us?!
But there's a catch!
You absolutely can't
open the gift at all!
If you get too nosy
and try and open it...
smoke will come out and
before you know it...
Poof! You'll be transformed
into a wrinkly old man
with a long beard
and everything!
What the heck kinda
reward is that?
Are you sure that turtle
is saying thanks?!
Wait, I've got it!
All you have to do is
not open the box, right?
Exactly. If you don't
open the box, you get
to eat delicious food
and spend some quality
time with a royal babe!
Hey, you idiots.
What do you think you're
whispering about over there?
Oh!
N‐nothing at all!
We were just discussing how
we were gonna ride this turtle
on over to Demon Island
to scout ahead.
We're gonna make sure those
villagers' story checks out!
See you later!
I think they're trying
to make this into a
different story.
Does it really matter?
(Splash)
[SHIROKAWA]
I can't breathe!
[SARASHINA]
You tryin' to kill me?!
[KUROSAKI]
I can't swim!
[SHIROKAWA]
Are you sure this boat's okay?!
[KUROSAKI]
What if we get
shipwrecked or somethin'?
We don't have
any food to eat!
Then I guess we'll just have
to eat the three of you.
Ah!
I knew it!
Pheasant! Hurry up and
go find Demon Island
before we get eaten!
Roger!
[SHIROKAWA]
I don't see any land...
[SARASHINA]
And the stupid pheasant
hasn't come back yet.
He obviously
abandoned you.
Huh?
Our bond is unbreakable!
You were ready to
sell each other out
when it looked like
you'd be eaten.
No, it can't be!
He left us!
He forgot all about us
and saved himself!
I'm hungry.
Me, too.
Oh.
Looks like I had
one left after all.
It's mine!
Let go!
Huh?
Aaagh!
Which one of these did you drop?
Was it this single,
tiny dumpling?
Or was it this stack of entry
cards for a sweepstakes to win
a year's supply of dumplings?
Or perhaps it was...
this winning entry card for a
Hokkaido Bounty of the Sea set
containing the highest quality
crab, sea urchin, salmon roe,
and scallops?
Uh... just the
normal dumpling.
I see. Yes.
You are indeed truthful.
For your honesty,
I shall instead give you
this winning entry card for the
Hokkaido Bounty of the Sea Set.
Where's a post office?
A village by the sea, about 30
miles north‐northwest of here.
When will we get it?
The drawing will be held
in one month,
and the winner
notified by mail...
She ran off.
Give us back that dumpling!
What in tarnation
are y'all eatin'?
Ah! Hey there,
Old Lady Shizuko!
We're havin' ourselves
some peach!
President... you asleep?
I you want to sleep,
I can stay awake for you...
So, no then...
Don't touch me.
Keep your distance.
The four of us may be
travelling together,
but I don't trust any of you
farther than I can throw you.
Especially YOU, Usui.
You're WAY too suspicious!
I'm not falling for that
circus leader act!
Okay then.
Do whatever you
want, I guess.
[KUROSAKI]
Heeeey! Heeeey!
Ah. Isn't that
the pheasant?
Hey!
Ah! He came back for us!
Help me! Help me!
Huh? It looks like he's
got some kinda rope
around him or something.
OH!
Help me!
They're gonna kill me!
Help me! Help me!
Oh look! He must've fallen
and been taken by that
lovely ship.
That was awfully
thoughtful of them.
[IGARASHI]
Well, well. Are those
your "friends" down there
in that piss‐poor
lookin' boat?
What a letdown.
Well since you don't
have nothin' to steal
I guess we're gonna have to find
another way to keep ourselves
entertained.
Oh!
How about...
You beg for your lives!
You stupid bird!
Why'd you get
captured by pirates?!
And you lead them
right to us!
Traitors!
Another turtle?!
Is that the same one as before?
Does that mean...?
We're getting a reward?!
If you promise not to
peek inside, I'll give
you a present, okay?
O‐okay!
No we can't look!
I bet it's another trick
to see if we're honest!
Is it just me or does it
seem like the story's
getting messed up again?
Does it really matter?
Huh?
I wonder what she's doing...
There's some strange guy
sleepin' in there!
Who the heck is he?!
Get outta here!
You bastards think you
can just ignore me
for some crappy mini‐story?
Well ignore THIS!
Goodness gracious,
that's a whole lotta peach.
Ain't it though?
Reckon we got lots more.
So go on and eat up!
N‐no more, please.
I've had enough of this.
Well. Cut my bullet
clean in half, didn't ya?
Interesting.
How 'bout you come up here?
C'mon! Don't keep me waitin'!
Guess I've got no choice, huh?
(Scared)
Wait, wait, don't
use that thing!
Where the heck did
that even come from?!
You should probably
cover your ears.
Huh?
[CREWMAN]
Ah! The ship's on fire!
Uh...
(Crew screaming)
[Kurosaki]
AHHH! IT'S HOT!
Somebody help me already!
[Usui]
I think we'd better
clear some distance.
[MISAKI]
Good idea.
Hmph. Those guys sure
are interesting.
Oh... Thank you.
It's no problem.
Still...
It's already morning, huh?
I'm so tired.
(Yawn)
Oh. Look.
Hm?
Looks like we've finally
reached our destination.
Demon Island!
Hey! Do we really stand a
chance against these guys?
We didn't even bring any
weapons with us, man!
Oh! I know exactly what to do
in a situation like this!
Run away and
never come back?
Ta‐daa!
A piece of straw?
With this we'll be able
to trade around
for a bunch of
different things.
If we trade it enough times
we'll end up with a
super powerful weapon!
Really?!
All right! Do you have
anything to trade, Pheasant?
Yeah!
Ta‐daa!
Okay! And you, Dog!
Yeah!
Ta‐daa!
All right,
anything else?
The only weapon we need...
is THIS right here!
We'll take them head‐on!
President, President.
Have a look at this.
I get it.
If we disguise ourselves
with these,
we'll be able to infiltrate
the demon hideout
and catch them off‐guard.
Anyway, sneaking in instead
of storming the place
will also put the women
in much less danger.
Of course, this could just be
some sort of enemy trap.
But this is our only
option, so let's go!
Then the three of us...
We'll go check things out
in our realistic forms.
We'll blend in to
our surroundings.
Woof woof.
Screech screech.
Ooo aaa.
[KUROSAKI]
And if it looks
like we're screwed,
we'll sneak out of here.
[SHIROKAWA]
How's it look?
Huh?
Th‐this is...!
[SHIROKAWA]
It's paradise!
It's a maid harem!
Don't forget what we're
here for, you three idiots!
Huh?
Let's hurry and get
these girls to safety
before the demons find us!
Huh? What's going on?
I guess she's
a new girl?
[THREE IDIOTS]
S‐so that means...
You're really a GIRL?!
I'm leaving
these fools here.
Damnit, where the hell
did Usui run off to?
I'm right here.
Welcome back home...
Master Usui.
Uh...
Usui... You...
What trickery is this?!
Hm? Did I not mention
I was a demon?
But I really am the leader
of Three Idiots Circus.
Shut up! I don't care
about that crap!
It was you who kidnapped these
young maidens, wasn't it?
Prepare to die,
you perverted demon!
Hold it right there, missy‐
you've got it all wrong.
Huh?
We weren't kidnapped‐
we came here
because we wanted to!
HUH?!
We just couldn't bear
to spend another minute
in that filthy village.
All the guys were pigs.
It sucked.
[HONOKA
When Mr. Usui showed up
we knew we had to follow him.
[SATSUKI]
This island is like
a dream come true!
[SUBARU]
It's cozy AND
well‐maintained!
[ERIKA]
Yeah, we're way happier here.
Basically, these women have
completely taken over my home,
and I can't get rid of them.
Oh, poor, poor, pitiful me.
So...
Why don't we date,
Miss President?
Let's leave this island
and go someplace fun.
How bout it?
Wh...
Why would I date
someone like you‐
Ooh!
Cutesy flowers!
"Why"?
Because...
Because when I'm
with you I feel alive.
Ah...
[Usui, narrating]
Thus, the two of them
became lovers, and‐
H‐hey hold on a minute!
You've got it all wrong!
Th‐this guy's just
some perverted freak,
I wouldn't go out with him.
Also, that outfit's
rather revealing.
Are you trying to seduce me?
I'm not!
I didn't want it to be in the
way so I cut the hem short.
Hey, cut that out!
Let go of me!
[Usui, narrating]
And the two of them set off
on a new adventure.
But that's another story.
The end.
Quit it...
don't touch me...
pervert!
Mr. Usui...
what exactly have you
been making her listen to?
She sounds like she's
having a nightmare...
A special bedtime story
made by me.
[Usui, narrating]
Incidentally, The Three Idiots
ended up becoming
food after all.
But that, too, is another story.
We get treated like food
right up till the very end?
I don't wanna get eaten!
What a cruel way to go!
[Usui, narrating]
Fine, then The Three Idiots
ended up making it out
alive and in one piece.
(Bark)
[Usui, narrating]
The dog became the pet
of Old Man Hanasaka
and was renamed "Pochi."
But...
[Usui, narrating]
The pheasant ate some of
the old woman's starch...
(Evil laugh)
[Usui, narrating]
And the monkey tricked a crab
to steal its rice ball...
Don't kill us!
[Usui, narrating]
The end, I guess.
[MISAKI]
I really don't like having my
dreams controlled by YOU, Usui.
[USUI]
But, ma'am, you're the
adventurous type.
You enjoyed it, didn't you?
[MISAKI]
When have I ever said
I'm adventurous?!
[SAKURA]
Misaki! Listen, listen!
[MISAKI]
What is it, Sakura?
You're more hyped up than usual.
[SAKURA]
There's this SUPER dreamy band!
You think so too,
right, Shizuko?!
[SHIZUKO]
No. I have no interest
whatsoever.
[SAKURA]
Let's throw an awesome party!
[SHIZUKO]
It looks like we'll be spending
time with the band members.
[MISAKI]
What was that? The band members?
[USUI]
Yeah, the band members.
Didn't you know?