You're the one person,
I'd never want to hate me.
Heh... There you go again.
You're always making fun of me.
You really piss me off... you
know that?
[MISAKI]
But, I'm... I'm so
grateful to you...
I wonder if I'll...
forget about that, too.
I still haven't repaid you...
for everything... for all the
things you've done for me...
[USUI]
That's fine. Even if
you never repay me,
I'll help you
whenever you need.
And I will make you fall in love
with me, over and over again.
[USUI]
Just leave it to your "Master."
Heh. N‐now you're just...
talking stupid... dummy.
[KANOU]
23 hours, 55 minutes.
Just five minutes were left to
go. But it would appear that I
am the victor.
Heh. So much for being
the president's knight
in shining armor, Usui.
Looks like this little game of
ours is over, now that she truly
hates you‐
Kanou.
You really want to
try "playing" with me?
[KANOU]
Ah! I‐It's no use bluffing!
You can't threaten me now.
A‐yu‐zawa's already fallen
asleep! And when she wakes up‐
Who said I was asleep, Kanou?
Listening to Usui carry on
like some pervert... just
made me even angrier.
There's no way I could've gone
to sleep even if I wanted to!
(shocked)
[MISAKI] Kanou!
[KANOU] Gah!
You've pushed me so far
that I couldn't care less
about why you hate girls...
[MISAKI]
But don't worry... cause
I know exactly how I'm
gonna make you pay.
(frightened)
[SHIROKAWA]
"Notice of Open Campus."
[KUROSAKI]
Oh, that thing? They do it
every year for the junior
high schoolers, and...
[CLUB MEMBER A]
The battle is almost upon us!
[CLUB MEMBER B]
Recruit men of honor!
[CLUB MEMBER C]
Find the next star player!
Well, looks like we've
got the day off.
It's really only to
promote club activities.
Guess we can head
home for the day.
Actually, it looks like
they're doing a lot
besides just club
activities this year.
"Seven mysteries"?
"Relaxation Areas"?
[TRIO]
Huh? "Cafeteria staff"?
[SAKURA]
This looks like fun!
Cafeteria stuff!
We certainly have a lot
of activities this year.
I'd like to make the
cafeteria into a cute place,
somewhere that the visiting
students can rest...
I want it to be a place that
the middle school girls can
really feel at home in.
Getting everything prepared
is gonna be tough,
so we'll need as many people as
we can get. Will you guys help?
[GIRL A]
Of course!
[GIRL B]
I'll try asking some of
the other girls, too.
Thanks a lot.
I can't wait to meet
all the new girls!
What kind of decorations
should we do?
We will also have to be
sure to keep the budget
in mind as well...
[MISAKI]
So... Well if you girls need
help with anything at all,
no matter how easy or difficult
or embarrassing it might be...
make sure to use
this guy right here.
(KANOU scared)
Everyone meet first‐year
student, Soutarou Kanou.
Due to a very poor life decision
on his part, he's now working as
my personal errand boy.
Hey! You're the guy we
saw in the hall other day.
You're always wearing
that hood, aren't you?
[GIRL C]
He must be the quiet type.
[SAKURA]
Thanks for giving
us a hand, Kanou.
[GIRL A] Thanks!
[SHIZUKO] Thank you very much.
[SAKURA]
Well, girls, what do you say
we go round up the others?
[GIRL A]
So, what should we do?
Hmph...
(school bell ringing)
[GIRL B]
Where should we start?
[GIRL C]
I say we dress as boys.
(GIRLS laughing)
[GIRL B] As boys?
[YUKIMURA]
Uhm, Kanou...? I'm not really
sure what's going on,
but Miss Ayuzawa said if
you do a good job today,
all will be forgiven.
Oh! By the way,
I'm Yukimura,
the vice president.
Ah! Where are you going, Kanou?
(demonic growling)
Kanou...
Hey, Kanou! Can you give us
a hand with these boxes?
[KANOU] Gaahhh!
[OTHERS] Huh?
(demonic growling and
KANOU freaking out)
[KOSUGI]
President, if we do that,
then this here will...
[MISAKI]
Fine. Use the chemistry room...
[KANOU, thinking]
Looks like she's finally gone.
Now's my chance to escape...!
(demonic growling)
[YUKIMURA]
Just how many Presidents are
there?! Did she make clones of
herself?
No, there's just
one... I think.
[MISAKI, thinking]
It's strange... Watching
Kanou like this, something
seems a little off.
True, he avoids girls, but
there's no hatred in his eyes.
It doesn't look like he's afraid
of them either.
[GIRL A]
I wonder if we can do something
about that wall over there...
[GIRL B]
Oh, yeah... probably so...
(GIRL stumbling and knocking
furniture around)
(GIRL gasps)
[KANOU] Oh...
[GIRL B]
I'm sorry! I tripped
on that chair.
[GIRL B] Thank you.
(KANOU embarrassed)
Misa's off
AGAIN today?
Idiot! We come here
whether Misa's here or not!
That's what true love's
all about! Idiot!
(sigh) Yeah,
that's true...
Even Usui's here today...
Hey sis, I brought you this.
It's some turmeric tea
and chestnut candy
I won in a contest.
Thanks. Just leave it
over there please.
[SUZUNA]
Are you getting ready for the
open campus?
It sounds like
a lot of fun.
Uh? Hey, Suzuna
what would make YOU
want to enroll in
a certain high school?
Well, it would definitely‐
Ah! And you can't say,
"One with a Sweepstakes
Club." Try and think of
something else, okay?
Something else.
[SUZANA] Something else...
Um... Ummm uh... Let's see...
[MISAKI] What could it be? What
could it be? What could it be?
One with a Gift
Application Club.
[MISAKI]
Guess I should've known better.
[YUKIMURA]
Kanou, a little
more to the right!
Oh, the left side is
drooping a little now.
It looks like you're
working hard, Kanou.
So it's finally
tomorrow, huh?
Misaki. Please
come take a look.
I'd like to use these...
for our cosplay costumes.
(MISAKI stunned)
[SAKURA] (giggles)
Aren't they great!
[SHIZUKO]
It took a lot of work
to get these prepared.
[GIRL A]
Our teacher said they
looked nice, too.
[SAKURA]
Are they no good, Misaki?
[MISAKI, thinking]
No... This... This could be
exactly what we need!
[MISAKI]
It's all right.
Wear these and do your best!
Yaay!
(excited chatter)
Next up is the school tour.
What's this? Looks like
it's split up into
different "courses."
Today our students
will serve as your
guides around campus.
[GIRLS] Huh?
[MISAKI] I'm sure you're all
interested in seeing different
things,
[ARAMAKI] Anyone interested in
[Misaki] so for each course
there's a different tour.
[KOSUGI] This way for fine arts!
[MISAKI] Please choose the one
that interests you the most!
[BOY] They even have a
"Relaxation Area" course.
[GIRL A]
Sounds like fun! Which
one should we do first?
[GIRL B]
And an "Explore the Seven
Mysteries" course.
[MISAKI]
And also, for anyone who doesn't
know what course to take
or wants to have an
all‐around tour, please
step right this way.
We're here to answer all
of your questions!
[BOY A]
Okay, Group 1 is moving out.
[BOY B]
Can we get some more
help over here?
Well, everyone‐ Whaddaya
say we head out too?
Time for the "Request and
Answers on Demand" course.
Okay!
Misa's not here today
either, this is the worst...
Yeah, there's no point in coming
if our sweet Misa isn't here...
How many times do I
have to say it?
We come whether she's here or
not, because that's true love!
Check it out!
Even Usui's...
[TRIO]
He's not here!
Oh, my. What's the
matter, Masters?
Are you feeling down today?
I think she's forgotten
all about us.
But we'll never
forget about her!
As an apology for Misa
being off for today,
you'll have the entire Maid
Latte staff here to wait on you.
(together)
We're at your service, Masters.
Please relax... and let us
know... if you need anything.
Is this real life?
I could die and
go to heaven!
I'm floating!
Also, as an extra special treat,
I'd like to introduce you to...
our lovely kitchen staff!
Thank you for being
such loyal customers.
Sorry, this is my first
time out on the floor.
I don't really know
what to say...
No, no, don't
worry about it.
Thank god. I was worried
that they had some strange
lifeform cooking back there.
Okay, you idiots!
Let's order up a storm!
I'm paying for this one!
And I'll write up how
I feel about it in the
customer guestbook!
Ooh, good idea!
Do your best, Ikkun!
Then I'll compose a poem
brimming with perversion‐
I mean, emotion and
Misa'll love it for sure!
Okay! Then I'll reflect
on all of my fondest memories
with Misa over and over
in my head! Woohoo!
What would you like
on your omelette today?
How about "You suck"?
You're being a nuisance to
the other Masters, so would
you please be quiet?
It would be great if you left
and never came back, Masters.
Isn't she the best?
(TRIO in awe)
She sure is.
Does anyone else get the
feeling she hates us...?
[HAGIMOTO]
The Second Mystery of Seika is,
sometimes, when no one's around,
you can hear a ghostly
tune coming from the
Broadcasting Room!
[MISAKI, thinking] Right now,
everything is running smoothly.
[GIRL] What's that all about?
A cursed song?
But... it looks like the sports
clubs are...
[BOY A] I'm telling you,
the sandbag is fun!
[BOY B] Nothing builds
closeness like tackling!
[BOY C] The ball is your friend!
[MISAKI, thinking]
...completely striking out. Uh?
Hey, you over there!
How rude. I'm not a stranger.
[Misaki] If you're just going
to stand around and do nothing
(GIRLS squealing)
then why even bother coming
to school on a day off?
Hey! I'm helping you
out right now by being
your pillar of support.
Don't you find my
presence reassuring?
MORE LIKE ANNOYING!
Your "presence" is way
too much of a distraction!
Can't you find somewhere
else to go?
(confused)
What do you want me to do about
it? It's not like it's my fault.
Hmmm... Actually, I just thought
of the perfect job for you.
[BOY A]
No one wants to be
friends with the ball...
[MISAKI]
Hey, soccer club cheer up!
Usui said he'd LOVE to be
friends with the ball!
Huh. That's news to me.
Usui wants to?
[BOY A] Well come on
down here with us!
[BOY B] Here, have a ball!
[BOY C] Show us a cool shot!
[BOY A] Hey junior high
students! If you want to see
something REALLY awesome come
over here!
[BOY B]Step right up!
[BOY C] Let's get you a uniform.
Huh? The soccer club?
They're using Usui to
help get new recruits?!
Our club needs him too!
(MOB screaming)
Well, guess that's that.
Make sure to help out the
sports clubs to the best
of your ability.
'Kay?
W‐wait just a minute! I
couldn't! I CAN'T greet
the visitors!
[GIRL A]
C'mon, don't say that.
[GIRL B]
Yeah, come on‐ we have a costume
ready for you and everything!
Y‐you girls just go on
and have fun without me!
We couldn't possibly do
something like that.
Yeah, after all, if
it wasn't for you
we never could've gotten
this done. Right?
[SAKURA]
Let's all have fun together!
[GIRL A]
You've helped us out
so much, Kanou.
[GIRL B]
Though you did run away
a lot at first...
[GIRL C]
Leave the customers to us‐
all you need to worry about is
setting the tables, Kanou.
[GIRL D]
And if anything happens, we'll
be here to back you up.
See! Look at what a good
time Yukimura's having!
Hm? Gahhhh!
Kanou...
Don't worry, Kanou. We've got
the perfect costume for you‐
you'll LOVE it... (evil giggles)
(KANOU freaking out)
(whistle blowing)
Come on everybody,
let's play soccer!
Be friends
with the ball!
Usui! Come over to
the baseball club next!
[BASEBALL Club, chanting]
Usui, Usui!
[MISAKI] Has everyone been
enjoying themselves so far?
[GIRL A] Yeah!
[GIRL B]
They let us mess around with all
the supplies in the art room,
and even showed us how to play
guitar in the music room.
I never imagined we'd
have so much fun!
I'm glad to hear it. Make
sure to enjoy your stay, okay?
[CROWD] Whoa! Huh?
[PING PONG MEMBER]
Please come to the
ping pong club!
(CROWD in awe)
[GIRL A]
All the tours end at the
cafeteria, don't they?
I thought you might be tired
from all that walking,
so this is your chance to
rest and ask any remaining
questions you might have.
Feel free to talk
to some of senior
students, too.
Okay!
Hey there, come on in!
Please take whichever
seat you'd like.
(in awe) It's just
like a maid café!
Make sure to rest up and have a
good time.
Misaki! Yaay!
What do you think?
Y‐You're so
cute, Sakura!
Misaki, you should
wear one, too!
Definitely not.
A‐anyway... It looks like
things are going great.
(cafeteria chatter)
Yeah, everyone's
having a good time!
Though to be honest, some
seem hesitant or afraid.
But if you just talk
to them a bit, they
open right up!
[SAKURA] C'mon, take
a little break!
[BOY] Oh, she's pretty nice.
At first I thought the boys
would simply laugh at us,
but they truly seem to be
enjoying themselves.
Not only them but
the girls as well.
It would be wonderful
if every day were like
this, wouldn't it?
Uh... It sure would...
Having a fun time together
is really wonderful,
don't you think?
(thinking) Yeah. Especially
like this... Right?
Well, I'm going to take another
look around, I'll see you guys
later‐
Oh, whoa!
(shock)
Don't you look
cute today, Kanou.
It's not my fault! I
was surrounded by girls
with no way to escape!
Oh really? You sure you're
not enjoying yourself?
YOU'RE WRONG! This
is exactly why I
can't stand girls!
How is this costume "perfect"
for me?
And what's with this stupid cap?
Why do I have to be a rabbit?!
What in the world are you
women thinking?! And what's
with all the maid outfits?
Are they always this
wishy‐washy?! I don't
understand it!
[KANOU] Just what kind
of creatures are they?!
[MISAKI, thinking] When it comes
to girls, this guy is...
[KANOU]
Women... Women are
just so breakable...
Kanou, seems you can
look us in the eye when
talking now. Heh.
Huh?
These past couple of days you
saw for yourself, didn't you?
[MISAKI]
Do you really think that's true?
Have the girls really been as
weak and fragile as you thought?
Kanou!
You don't have to run
away anymore, Kanou.
This is the first time...
I've ever been around girls
like this.
[BOY] Point!
(KENDO CLUB cheering)
[JR. HIGH BOY] Dammit!
[KENDO CLUB] Don't go looking
down on us high schoolers!
Usui! Come to
our club next!
No, ours!
(CLUBS arguing)
(silence)
[USUI]
I've had enough.
(CLUBS stunned)
[BOY]
O... okay...
[GIRL A]
Maybe we should go with Seika.
Huh? A‐are you girls thinking
about enrolling at Seika?!
That's wonderful!
[MISAKI]
So you like it here?!
Yes! Uh, but I... Oh, gosh!
[MISAKI]
Wh‐What is it?
[GIRL A]
The truth is, I'm not
very good with boys.
They're kinda scary.
[GIRL B]
She's only ever been in
all‐girls environments.
[GIRL C]
The only reason she came today
was because we asked her to.
[GIRL A]
There are a lot of boys
at Seika, aren't there?
I wish it was a
girls‐only school...
[YOUNG KANOU]
Dad! What do you mean,
Mom "broke" and went away?
[KANOU'S FATHER]
Soutarou! Women are
more delicate and
fragile than you think!
You gotta
watch how you handle women,
or they'll break on you.
(sobbing)
Mooom!
If they're gonna break,
I'll never go near them again!
[YOUNG KANOU] Girls are scary!
[KANOU] I understand.
I understand now.
[KANOU]
My mom didn't "break"...
She was just sick of the
way my father treated her,
so she left...
I've known... the whole time!
[SAKURA]
Oh, there you are!
Hey, Kanou!
Come here for a minute.
[KANOU] But right now, I'm‐
[SAKURA] It's fine, just
come on!
[KANOU, thinking]
I've known this for
a long time now...
Still, I didn't think
I could go near them.
(YOUNG KANOU crying)
[KANOU] If I got too close...
I thought something painful
would happen, like back then.
Because women are
weak and fragile.
[MISAKI]
Have these girls really been as
weak and fragile as you thought?
Guys are no good, huh? That
does make things pretty tough...
[MISAKI] Okay then.
[GIRLS] Huh?
Is THIS guy scary?
[KANOU] Uh...
[GIRL A] Oh! Well...
[MISAKI]
Hey, Bunny Boy!
Show them you're not scary!
[MISAKI] Take a good look.
[KANOU] AH! Huh?
You see? He's not scary at all.
Right?
Uh, yeah...
[MISAKI]
You don't have to
run away anymore.
[KANOU] Very well.
[MISAKI] Huh?
(HAPPY)
Ahhh!
I will now cast a magic spell.
Please close your eyes.
Listen to my voice.
From now on you are...
(thinking) I am...
(spoken) ...no longer afraid!
(clap)
(GIRL chuckling)
(GIRLS laughing)
It worked! I don't feel
scared at all! Heh.
[GIRL B] That's
cause it's magic!
[GIRL A] Yeah...
[GIRL C] That was cute!
[GIRL B] Mhmmm
[GIRL C] And those bunny
ears are funny!
(courtyard chatter)
Looks like you know some cute
magic tricks, don't you...
...Bunny Boy?
Oh, once you're done with
that, you can head out.
Okay.
[MISAKI]
Kanou, good job today.
As promised, everything
is forgiven.
Be safe on your way home 'kay?
Um, Miss Presi‐!
Huh?
You did a good job, too...
Uh... Thanks for your hard
work, we couldn't have done
it without you.
[MISAKI]
I wonder where we're going... I
wonder if you'll let me down...
I wonder why you won't say
anything... Uh, Usui?
(hitting the ground) Gah!
[USUI]
Feeling satisfied?
With your punishment.
Uh, yeah, that's already
taken care of...
Oh, really? Then maybe you
wouldn't you mind giving
ME a little thanks, too.
You didn't come check on me
once. Man, I'm exhausted.
Well‐ if it wasn't for
you Usui the sports clubs
would've crashed and burned!
You really saved the day!
And for that I'm very grateful!
Mhmm...
No good?
That doesn't make me
feel better at all.
Can't you think of something
that would make YOU happy?
Uh... eeeeeeeh?!
[USUI] Huh?
[MISAKI] You...
You did very well today.
Ayuzawa...
[USUI]
So can I ravage you now?
You idiot!
(whining)
[KANOU]
Yukimura...
Out of everyone, I really do
respect you most of all.
I can't believe not a
single person noticed
you're really a man.
You've got it wrong, Kanou!
I want to change, but I can't
find my uniform!
[SAKURA]
Sparkly!
[MISAKI]
I'm always so busy, it's a
wonder I'm still awake, huh?
[USUI]
Maybe it'd be best if Kanou
hypnotized you again.
[USUI]
This guy hasn't slept
for nearly a month.
[KANOU]
Very perceptive of you.
Now then, here goes.
[MISAKI]
Hey now! Don't do it, Kanou!
[SUZUNA] Ta‐daa!
[MISAKI] Whoa, Suzuna!
[SUZUNA]
To get right to it, next time
will be a story about summer.
[SATSUKI]
Misa! We're going to the beach
with everyone from Maid Latte!
Does everyone have
their bikinis ready?
(MAIDS enthusiastically
answering)
[SATSUKI]
Usui, act as our
bodyguard, okay?