Huh? Ma'am, you have
an older brother?
Mm‐hmm. But he's married
and has a kid,
so I don't get to see him
very often anymore.
Huh.
(Doorbell)
Welcome back, Mas‐
Oh... My Lady.
[CUSTOMER]
So cute!
[MISAKI]
Allow me to show you in.
[CUSTOMER]
That's no ordinary girl!
Yeah, I'm sure of it!
Excuse me, ma'am!
But are you...
by any chance Aoi?!
[BOY]
Oh! Aoi?!
[AOI]
My goodness.
I never imagined
I would have so many fans.
[BOY]
You really are her?
Aoi...
is so happy!
(Boys very excited)
[BOY]
Oh! It's really Aoi!
[SATSUKI]
What's going on over here?
Oh, Aunt Satsuki.
Aoi, it's you?!
[SATSUKI]
You want to work here?!
The boss's niece?
Her older brother's
daughter, apparently.
She's so cute!
What on Earth are you thinking?!
Of course you can't work here!
Why not?
What do you mean "why not"?!
You're still in middle school!
It's against the law.
And what about your
responsibilities?
I'm on a break
right now.
Ugh!
I've actually
been disowned again!
Wow, talk about
an incredible retort.
Ah!
Ma'am!
How incredibly exhibitionist.
The number of site visits
is kind of scary.
So does this mean she's
going to be staying with
you for a little while?
Yeah, I called my brother
earlier and he was still pretty
mad about the whole thing.
[AOI]
Oh!
I knew it would look good!
It suits me, right?
When can I start?
I only lent you that because
you kept whining that you
wanted to try one on.
You saw how popular I am!
With me here, you'll get
even more customers!
After all, right now
I'm the most famous
of all Internet idols!
And all men are absolutely
powerless against my spell.
Oh! I'd better take some
pictures for my blog.
We have a strict policy
the prohibits anyone
other than our employees
from wearing
one of our costumes.
Come on, just a selfie!
We might start getting
visits from customers
who think this is some kind
of costume rental shop.
Apparently, some other cafes
offer that service.
Hmph! Whatever‐
This dress looks
way better on me
than it does on
some girl off the street!
[SATSUKI]
Aoi!
What, you got a problem?!
I'm way cuter than you are,
so why can't‐
You're very cute.
But no picturess allowed, okay?
Well, time to get to work.
Make sure to change
out of those, okay Aoi?
(Doorbell)
Wah!
Misa.
I'm back...
Welcome back, uh... Master.
[CUSTOMER]
Aoi's in a maid outfit!
It really suits her!
Aoi! What are you doing?!
Thank you!
Wait! Wait!
[AOI]
I knew it.
Out of all of them, I'm‐
Huh?
A new worker?
That's the boss' niece.
I told her she had
to change, but...
Who is that, Satsuki?
Who's that man that's
covered in pheromones?!
That man oozes sex appeal
from every pore!
Uh, well he's...
Getting a man like that
to fall for me
would be like
winning a trophy.
But Aoi, Usui and Misa
are kinda, y'know‐
They're going out?!
No, I don't think they're
actually together... yet.
Manager! Manager!
Manager!
The cook just called
to say she is sick
and can't come in
for her shift tonight!
Huh? I already have my
hands full with Aoi!
[AOI] There's no need to worry.
Why did it have to be
today of all days?!
[AOI] A girl of such low caliber
could never be a threat to ME.
I've already called
everyone, trying to find
someone who can cover,
but no one's available!
Manager, is everything okay?
It's terrible!
We don't have a cook
and it's about to be
our busiest time!
Misa, can you cook?!
Please, we need your help!
Uh...
Should I help, too?
Huh?!
Huh? YOU, Usui?
Of course.
Leave the cooking to me.
B‐but we can't just use some
customer from the store!
Usui, get your butt in there!
But ma'am!
But first, you must pass
the omelette test!
Understood.
[SATSUKI]
Okay. You'll be judged by
your rice omelette.
The ingredients and amounts
are already laid out for you.
[MISAKI] Ma'am, can you please
just think about it‐
[SATSUKI] We have no
other choice!
[SATSUKI]
Go, Usui!
Well, here I go.
Whooa!
Woooooow!
[SATSUKI]
This omelette has the creamiest
eggs I've ever tasted...
[MISAKI]
Delicious!
You pass!
Gee, thanks.
(Giggles)
You cook just like
a professional.
Could you make something
just for me?
Sure, if you order it
from the café menu.
Aoi, this guy is completely
depraved. Just ignore him.
You're so cruel, Misa.
But it excites me when you
insult me like that.
Don't touch me you freak!
Yes, yes.
Looks like Misa's
not here today.
Maybe we should
just go home...
(Doorbell)
Uh... What's this?!
Who's that?
It's Aoi, the famous net idol!
[SHIROKAWA]
You know her?
Geez, Ikkun, not only are you
a closet‐nerd but a fanboy, too.
So when you say "net idol"...
You mean she posts
a bunch of sexy pics?
Sounds like it's right up
your alley, Kurotatsu.
NO! Aoi is a
pure‐hearted angel!
But she does also have a bit of
a mischievous side, too!
Waaa! Ooh!
[AOI]
See, no man can resist me.
So why doesn't...?
(Doorbell)
Welcome back, Master.
Hm?
Will you make a special
omelette just for me today?
I'm a customer today.
Then why don't we sit together?
No, thank you.
[CUSTOMERS]
What a waste!
[USUI]
I haven't sat upstairs
in a while...
That man... He's gotta have
some sort of weakness!
I refuse to accept that he
prefers that unrefined
girl over me...!
Huh? Hey, Aoi.
Misa, you can just
set those anywhere.
Got it.
The manager is out
right now, Aoi...
So? What're you
telling me for?
Uh... She should be
back soon, so you can
just have a seat and wait.
Just butt out.
Aoi, do you hate me?
Oh, whatever would
give you that idea?
Guess there's nothing
I can do. I'll just
leave her alone.
Feel free to do
whatever you want.
Wait! I want to ask
you something‐!
Uh?
What is it?
Y‐you're changing clothes.
Yeah. I'm done
for the day.
Hmm?
THOSE are your clothes?
Huh? Well, yeah.
You don't have a
shred of femininity!
Uh...
And you call yourself a woman?
Are these even girls' clothes?
Are they men's?!
I don't know. I just pick
whatever's cheapest...
You look tragic!
Don't you even want to be cute?!
I don't really care
about things like that.
(Sigh)
How did someone like you
manage to seduce Takumi Usui?
You have some secret
technique, don't you?!
Huh?
That's the only
logical explanation‐
after all no one can
resist my charms!
Besides, if I could catch
a man like that,
my cuteness would
become unstoppable!
Tell me right now!
What method did you use, woman?!
I didn't use any "method",
and I didn't "seduce" him!
Don't lie to me!
J‐just calm down...!
Here we go‐ Upsy‐daisy!
Ahh!
You super‐strong freak!
Uhh...
Will you let me try your
special rice omelette today?
Move it.
I'm going on break now.
See you in a bit.
What do you want from me?
I want you to be mine,
and mine alone.
Oh really?
Do you really know the
meaning of the words
you're saying, little girl?
(Gasp)
(Thud)
Huh?
What the...?
What the hell do you think
your doing, you freak?!
(Crash)
Huh?
Aoi...
That's enough of this!
What was that for?!
What are you thinking,
doing something like that?!
Quit trying to one‐up yourself!
Everyone already knows
how cute you are,
so why are you
doing this?
What exactly are you
trying to prove?!
Because they all
laughed at me!
Just because
I liked cute things!
But if I can make enough
people think I'm cute,
I'll finally be able to
get back at them!
Do you really believe that?
If you really want to get back
at them, then face them head‐on!
Be strong enough to take them
on alone, without dragging
anyone else into it!
I don't know what
you've gone through,
but I do know that
the people who laughed
at you back then
are sure to acknowledge...
how cute you
really are, Aoi.
Even if...
you're a boy.
What the...?
(Sigh)
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you...
But he would've gotten
super mad at me if I did.
You knew it the first time
you saw me, didn't you?
Is that true?
That's why he rejected me.
Huh?! Then what'd you
attack him for?
I just did exactly what
you told me to do and
confronted him face to face.
Shut up,
you pervert!
[USUI] Were you jealous, Misa?
[AOI] What a couple of weirdos.
[AOI] I figured they'd be
more surprised.
[MISAKI] Like hell! What is
there to be jealous about?!
Even though I'm a boy,
I like cute things,
and dressing up like a girl.
It's only natural that people
would laugh and be surprised.
Huh? What would
we laugh for?
When we found out,
we were a little
surprised, but...
those clothes
looked good on you!
Aoi, you've had enough
fun for one day, right?
Don't you think
it's time you...
I'm leaving.
Next time...
I'll be so perfect that
EVERYONE will fall at my feet!
He missed the point!
Looks like we're back
to square one.
I won't forget about
this, you weirdos!
What's with that
uppity parting shot?!
He completely ignored
what I told him!
Not quite...
I wonder if Aoi will
come today, too...?
I really hope she does...
My apologies for
the wait, Masters.
Ah!
These guys over here were
cheating on you with Aoi!
Wh‐what are you saying?!
I only have eyes
for you, Misa!
Oh look at the time‐
guess you better be
on your way, Masters.
Ah!
But we only just got here!
[MISAKI]
See you later, Masters.
Ahh!
(Gasp)
[SATSUKI]
Aoi, it's perfect!
A school uniform?! Good job!
Very, very, VERY good!
What a cute little
middle‐school boy you are!
Please dress like this
forever and ever and ever!
The only reason I'm in this
is because I don't have
anything else to wear.
Don't have anything
to wear? Why?
Satsuki, hurry up and give me
some of your old outfits‐
I need something decent to wear.
I'm guessing my brother threw
you out again, didn't he?
So Aoi's clothes were
actually hand‐me‐downs
he got from you?
That's right.
I did all of the alterations
and tailoring myself.
Wow‐ that's amazing!
You know how to sew, Aoi?
That's a great way
to save money.
(Shocked)
Thanks for all your
hard work today, Misa.
See you tomorrow.
You're dressed like that AGAIN?
Don't you understand how much
potential you're wasting?!
I can't take it anymore!
Come with me‐ NOW!
Bye bye!
Good luck, Misa.
Pink camisoles,
lace miniskirts...
sleeveless chiffon tops,
and loose balloon skirts!
Those are the kinds of clothes
that have "cuteness" written
all over them!
How can you not be
interested in things
like that?! Huh?
Uh, well I'm sorry...
Your lack of personal style,
your nonexistent fashion sense,
and your inability to put
effort into your appearance
is killing you
and pissing me off!
This is starting to feel
more like a personal attack
than a makeover...
Looks like I have no choice.
It's up to me to find you
some suitable clothes.
Wait a minute, Aoi!
I can't! I don't have
any money for clothes!
That's super cheap!
Lucky! I needed
a new notebook!
Uh...
Hello there, would you
like a free sample?
Free?! How many
can I take?
[GIRL] Just one, please.
Sorry, sorry. So, what
were we doing again?
Forget it.
Just hurry up already.
These're on sale right now.
But I can cut the price
if you buy a dozen!
Croquettes are my
sister's favorite!
[AOI]
I should've known trying
to give you a makeover
was a waste of time!
[MISAKI]
So, you went to school today?
If I stayed home,
I'd just feel smothered.
But, I guess it's
the same at school, too.
Why's that?
All they ever do is insult
all the things I like.
When it comes to things
that are pretty or cute...
Apparently, I'm not
allowed to like them,
because that's not what
boys are supposed to like.
That's why everyone hates me!
Why no one will ever like me!
[MISAKI]
Really? But I like you a lot.
Huh?!
I think your personality's
refreshing, Aoi.
Yeah, well I hate you,
you man‐woman!
(Laughing) I know.
D‐don't tell me‐ are you
actually a masochist?!
You seem like a sadist!
Huh?
Look, I'm not into any of
that weird stuff, got it?!
Don't say that
kind of thing so loudly...!
This sucks.
Why does the weatherman
always get it wrong?
Aoi, don't you have
a handkerchief
or something?
I have one, but I
don't want to use it.
It's my favorite,
the design's super cute.
Hmm...
I guess I'll just have to
wipe you off with mine then!
[WOMAN]
Hey! Help me someone!
That man stole my purse!
Stop right there!
Hand it over, or else!
Huh?! What does she
think she's doing?!
If you're not going to stop,
then I guess I'll have
to MAKE YOU!
Ah!
(Police sirens)
That guy was HUGE,
but you took him on anyway!
For a girl you're
way too reckless!
Because I'm not a "normal" girl?
Or because for a woman,
I'm "too strong and too manly"?
Sorry but that's just
the kind of person I am.
I didn't meant
to make you worry.
A lot of people
get angry at me for it;
they tell me I need
to be more ladylike.
But, I think it's better to be
the person who you really are,
in my opinion...
That's the kind of excuse
I'd expect from a girl
who doesn't even
know the meaning of
the word "feminine"!
Uh...
If you don't clean
yourself up a bit,
you'll cry when he
abandons you in the end.
Uh... When who does?
Takumi Usui.
We don't have that
kind of relationship.
But he likes you.
No, he doesn't!
He just enjoys
making fun of me!
That guy's a weirdo.
Y'know, somehow
I can't help but feel
sorry for the guy...
Huh?
It's nothing at all.
AH! Your sleeve is ripped!
Oh... Oh no!
That's what you get
for buying cheap crap.
Tell me your size.
Huh?
I'll make you something.
Make me something?
You mean, like clothes?
Yeah.
Hey!
You've got good looks at least,
so I'll figure something out.
No, that's okay!
I'm doing it!
I said it's fine!
(Gasps)
Uh... Somehow this seems
a little off, right?
You got a problem with
my sense of style?!
But you look
so cute, Misa!
Maybe we could do
a Lolita Day...
You look
surprisingly cute...
That's for sure!
What're you looking at?!
Just laugh and get it over with!
If you've got something
to say, then say it!
Whenever you're embarassed
you get really animated
and look even cuter
than normal.
[MISAKI]
Get out of here,
you stupid pervert!
[MISAKI]
It sure is hard wearing
clothes you're not used to.
Wait, didn't you and
the others take some photos?
[SATSUKI]
Of course! Click, click!
I took lots of photos that
will serve as keepsakes!
[AOI]
It's because I made it.
It really suited her, huh?
[USUI]
Yeah. I got really excited.
[MISAKI]
Shut up Usui, you idiot!
[HONOKA]
I forgot! I have to get to the
mall before it closes. See you!
[MISAKI]
Good night, Honoka.
[SUBARU]
I have to get to
my next job, so...
[MISAKI]
That's fine, Subaru.
I'll stay behind.
[USUI]
I'm a little worried.
[SUBARU]
Misa, I'm sorry.