¶¶
( Lord boros yells )
( Groans )
Even though my true power
has been unleashed on you,
somehow,
you're still able to keep up.
Saitama: Yep.
You're tough. Cool.
Tank-top master:
Putting city a back together
might be impossible.
I'll think about that later.
Right now, I should be
focused on the battle.
She may be way up
at rank two or whatever,
but I can't just leave
everything to one little girl.
I happen to have my own ways
of fighting enemies in the air.
Like this!
( Yells )
Tornado: Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
( Tank-top master yells )
Tornado: This area's got
some nice rubble to play with.
Get out of my way,
and let me do so.
Tank-top master: S-she's using
her psychic power?!
I give up!
¶¶
Alien: Oh, no!
We're under attack again!
Alien #2: Return fire!
Alien #3: We can't!
The guns are completely jacked!
Alien #4: Seriously?!
Then we're all dead meat!
Alien #5: This planet's
too tough to steal from!
Alien #6: Lord boros, save us!
Gunner: I just wanna go home.
Genos: Such incredible power.
Tornado may actually
bring it down on her own.
Drive knight: I have
some errands to run.
Therefore,
I will be heading out now.
Things appear
to be under control.
Child emperor: Sure.
Go ahead then.
Some of the other heroes
have already left, too.
Drive knight: Before I go,
genos, have you got a second?
There's something
I wish to tell you.
Genos: Drive knight,
class s, rank nine.
This is a first.
Drive knight: Listen.
Metal knight
is actually your enemy.
( Genos gasps )
Drive knight: Be careful.
Genos: What do you mean?
Drive knight:
You will know soon enough,
but for now,
stay away from him.
¶¶
( melzargard laughs )
( Laughs )
Atomic samurai: Bastard.
You sure are making things
interesting around here.
( Melzargard laughs )
I'm beginning to taste victory.
- ( Bang groans )
- Melzargard: Huh?
Bang: Ah, that's better.
The stiffness in my shoulders
is gone.
Guess I'm a little rusty.
Melzargard: No.
How can you still be alive?
Atomic samurai: Hey.
Forgetting something?
Atomic slash!
Melzargard: Insolence.
Such complete insolence!
Bang: You move
that heart-marble-thing around
inside your body
in order to hide its location,
but your regeneration process
always begins with your head.
Therefore, in the center
of that must lie...
Your heart.
After seeing it
happen so many times,
even a monkey
could figure it out.
See? Checkmate.
Melzargard: No!
( Marble shatters )
( Groans )
Iairon: Silverfang!
Atomic samurai: All I needed
was one more swing.
Keep your hands to yourself,
and let me finish
what I start, silverfang.
Bang: My goodness.
I really need to do
more full-body workouts.
Puri-puri prisoner:
We got all the heads.
That was the last one.
Victory is ours!
Metal bat: Yeah,
but there's still
that big-ass ship up there
to deal with.
( Explosions echoing )
Lightning Max: Okay.
I believe this is
the last
of the reported survivors.
Let's move.
Stinger: Yeah, sure.
Lightning Max: Mumen!
Quit your staring, and come on!
Mumen rider: Right! Coming!
¶¶
( lord boros yells )
( Singing in Japanese )
Lord boros: Nice moves.
As I thought, you are strong.
Of the myriad beings
I have battled thus far,
only you survived
for this long!
( Yells )
Now to release
the destructive energy
held within me!
Any normal creature hit by it
would find
even their bones vaporized!
( Singing in Japanese )
- Lord boros: Behind you!
- Saitama: Huh?
( Singing in Japanese )
Lord boros: You were
a worthy opponent,
but the outcome
of this battle is clear.
My species won
the struggle for survival
amid the harsh environment
of our home world.
We possess the ultimate
in regenerative abilities.
I in particular
have the godlike traits
of self-healing,
physical prowess,
and latent energy
beyond your conception.
A wound
that would be fatal for you
heals on me in mere moments.
By focusing all my energy
on my destroyed arm,
I can exponentially speed up
the healing process.
Good as new.
You, on the other hand,
will only get injured more,
all while your stamina
gradually decreases down to--
- saitama: Shut up.
- Lord boros: Huh?
Saitama: Blah, blah, blah.
You're boring me out of my mind.
Are you finished?
Not yet!
( Chorus singing )
Meteoric burst!
Saitama: Uh...
( Crew scream )
¶¶
Lord boros: The energy
shunted from my body
transforms
into a propelling force...
Elevating speed and power
to a level
beyond the limitations
of living flesh!
¶¶
( Music ends )
( Silence )
( Muted boom )
( Lord boros panting )
Doing this places
enormous stress on my body,
similar to anaerobic exercise.
As a result,
it shortens my life.
Therefore, it should
only be used as a trump card
for settling fights as quick--
Metal bat: It's tilting!
Blackluster: Nice!
You're doing it!
Awesome work, tornado!
( Footsteps )
¶¶
saitama: Cool.
I made it back.
Lord boros:
This infuriating man...
Makes me want to give this
everything I've got!
( Yelling )
¶¶
( gags )
( Coughs )
That's the way, saitama.
You are indeed
worth the effort.
( Saitama calmly )
Consecutive normal punches.
( Lord boros stammers )
¶¶
I will defeat you!
All my energy will be released,
blasting you...
And this planet
straight to hell!
Collapsing star,
roaring Cannon!
Saitama: In that case,
I'll use my own final move.
Killer move, serious series...
Serious punch.
¶¶
( Music ends )
( Wind blowing )
Lord boros: Did I lose?
I can feel nothing.
Saitama: You're still conscious.
You really are strong for real.
Lord boros:
The prophecy held true.
The battle was...
A hard-fought one.
Saitama: Yeah.
It sure was.
¶¶
lord boros: You lie.
You were holding back,
weren't you?
I never stood a chance.
It wasn't even a battle.
You obliterated me. Heh heh.
So much
for the words of prophecies.
You were just too strong.
Sai...tama.
¶¶
Tornado: It's crashing?
Genos: Is this master's doing?
Alien #1: The power sphere's
been broken!
Alien #2: We're going down!
Alien #3: Lord boros
let loose his full power!
- Alien #4: Get out! Get out!
- Alien #5: Run!
Alien #6: Stop shoving, stupid!
Gunner: I just wanna go home!
Mama!
- Iairon: It's coming down.
- Metal bat: Huh?
Hey, we better get outta here.
Bang: Whoa, this is bad.
Run for the association hq.
Atomic samurai:
Iai, hold on to me!
Iairon: I'm okay, master!
Atomic samurai: Damn it!
How did old man silverfang
get so fast?
Iairon: Now's not the time
to be competitive.
Puri-puri prisoner: Angel dash!
Metal bat: Hey, pansy,
don't you run in front of me!
You're too slow!
Puri-puri prisoner: Angel dash!
Metal bat: Stop calling out
your stupid moves, and just run!
Aliens: We're gonna crash!
Genos: It is down.
Blackluster:
All right, let's go.
¶¶
amai mask: How did city a
end up like this?
All of class s
was meeting here today.
Hmm?
Care to enlighten me
on this, metal bat?
Metal bat: Huh?
Amai mask: Explain it to me
so I can understand.
Metal bat:
Handsome kamen amai mask.
Where in the hell
did you pop up from?
Amai mask:
I was filming a TV drama
in the next town over.
There was a loud roar
and tremors,
so I came
to check things out,
only to find city a destroyed.
Metal bat: Monsters
on this big-ass ship behind me
came and attacked us.
They fired artillery
and did all this,
but we still took care of it.
( Amai mask sputters )
"Took care of it," you say?
Really?
You call this devastation
victory?
What utter incompetence!
I'm completely appalled
at all of you!
Metal bat: Hey...
You didn't even show up
until this was over,
so get off your high horse.
Amai mask: Yes, it's true
I didn't make it here in time.
But every single one
of you did, correct?
And you didn't even
save one brick!
Atomic samurai:
We were having a meeting
inside the headquarters building
when it all started.
We went outside as soon as we
heard the enemy attacking,
but the city had already
been reduced to ruins.
Amai mask: And? So what?
You think if you say that,
the media will just let this go?
Puri-puri prisoner:
Hey, handsome,
whose side are you on here?
We worked together
and did our best.
Amai mask: I'm on the side
of peace and justice.
Having class-s heroes
this clueless and pathetic...
Is an embarrassment.
Anybody that's this useless
should voluntarily retire.
Metal bat: Hey!
Don't start talking crap
with us, pretty boy!
Who's gonna care
about a pop idol
with his face up his ass?!
Amai mask: Do you have any idea
why I don't move up to class s?
It's simple, really.
I remain class a, rank one
so I can prevent
weak, good-for-nothing pissants
like you from ever moving up.
Nice timing, metal knight.
So you skip the meeting
and just now decide to show up?
¶¶
metal knight: This is...
Magnificent.
- Genos: Metal knight!
- Metal knight: Hmm?
Genos: What exactly
are you doing here?
The battle is already over.
Drive knight: Listen.
Metal knight
is actually your enemy.
Metal knight: Genos, right?
Genos: Do not tell me
you have come
to recover the spaceship.
Are you here to create
more powerful weapons
by incorporating
alien technology?
Metal knight: Precisely.
Powerful weapons
are a necessity
for the sake
of maintaining peace and order.
Amai mask:
Even with powerful weapons,
in the hands of heroes
like these, they'd be wasted.
Metal bat: That's it.
You're goin' down, pretty boy,
so watch your ass.
Blackluster: Yo!
I found some alien survivors!
Alien #1: Crappity-crap!
I thought lord boros never lost.
Alien #2: I know, right?
Think they're gonna kill us?
Alien #3: Maybe we can
talk our way out of this.
They seem reasonable.
Alien #6: Agh!
I'm so hungry, you guys!
Gunner: You idiot! Now's not
the time for--( Gasps )
- Shh! I hear someone coming.
- ( Footsteps )
Blackluster: What?!
Amai mask, why did you do that?
Amai mask: They did not deserve
to live. They were evil.
I merely implemented
justice swiftly. That's all.
I'm sure you understand,
don't you, genos?
You've been busy
since the exam,
but after the deep sea king
and today...
You've mostly been
a disappointment.
Bang: Leave it be.
Genos: Do not worry. I am fine.
He reminds me of how I was
before I met master,
a man on the edge
too eager to eliminate evil.
Just like me,
he must have gone through
something terrible in his past.
( Gasps )
Wait! Where is master saitama?
- ( Rumble )
- Tornado: Mm?
Saitama: Cool. Out for real.
Tornado: Hey!
Where'd you come from?
No way a class-b like you
would be inside that ship.
Genos: There you are!
Glad you are safe, master!
Saitama: Oh! Hey, genos!
We're done here. Let's go.
Genos: Were you able
to defeat their leader?
Saitama: Yeah.
He was really strong, too,
maybe the strongest
I've ever faced.
Genos: I see.
So without you, master,
the prophecy about
the destruction of the earth
- would have come true.
- ( Tornado gasps )
- Genos: Once again...
- Tornado: They're ignoring me?
Saitama: Nah.
It's these prophecies.
Turns out
you can't trust them at all.
- Tornado: Hold it right there!
- Saitama: Huh?
Tornado: I have no idea
how you did it,
but you went in the ship
on your own?!
You're just a class b.
How dare you butt in like that?
I didn't need you. I could
have handled it by myself!
Baldy! Octopus! Boiled egg!
Light bulb!
Avocado! Lame face...
Saitama: Hey, genos,
say something to her.
Genos: Sir.
Look, spoiled brat,
shut up, and get lost,
or pay the price.
Saitama: That's it! Yeah!
Tornado: Unforgiveable.
So I'm a brat, huh?
I'm older than you,
metal jackass!
Saitama: Whoa! Genos!
You're next, class-b baldy!
Bang: That's enough, tornado.
This sort of behavior isn't
becoming of a hero, now, is it?
Tornado: Uh...
Hmph!
Whatever.
Bang: Why are there
so many pigheaded troublemakers
amongst the elite heroes?
Saitama: Hey, genos,
your--your joints are
all bent the wrong way.
Here. I'll fix you up.
Oh, sorry. Your arm came off.
( Bang groans )
My back is killing me.
¶¶
genos: City a was
completely wiped off the map.
The arrival of aliens
and city a's annihilation
were history-making events
and were
the top stories for days,
but eventually
the coverage died down.
After that, no one mentioned
the city that had disappeared.
Metal knight
salvaged the spaceship.
Soon thereafter,
the hero association
headquarters was reconstructed
and became an impenetrable
fortress of steel.
The infrastructure was rebuilt
with new roads
leading out of h.Q.
This allowed heroes the ability
to deploy quickly to every city.
Heroes class a and above
were given the option
to live at headquarters,
letting them do
what they do best.
( Singing in Japanese )
Reporter:
You can see it clearly!
The entire building's
has been ripped out
down to the foundation!
Based on initial reports,
the monster appeared in city z.
Now city y--( Shrieks )
( Monster breathing deeply )
¶¶
( growls )
You humans waste your existence
in decadence and gluttony,
littering the earth
with worthless objects.
- ( Boy crying )
- Pluton: Now you shall rot
in the depths of the underworld
that spreads
below my mighty snout!
Who do we have here?
Genos: Who, you ask?
A great man
who is a hero for fun
and profit.
Pluton: A great man. Hmm?
¶¶
genos: With his disciple.
( Boy gasps )
Saitama: Oh, come on!
I'm back to one punch again?!
Damn it!