Genos: You are one
of the seafolk, correct?
Deep sea king: What if I am?
You must be another soldier
who's come to try and stop--
genos: I am here
to eradicate you.
( Deep sea king groans )
( Screams )
( Rain sizzling )
( Crowd murmurs )
Genos: Target eliminated.
Was that the last of them?
( Crowd gasps )
( Cheering )
Genos: They must have
been quite desperate.
( Deep sea king roars )
( Crowd gasping )
Deep sea king: Now I'm angry.
I will tear you to shreds.
Genos: I let my guard down.
Why do I never learn?
¶¶
supervisor: Saitama.
You're class c, rank two.
Are you sure about this?
Saitama: Yeah.
Hurry it up. It's raining.
Supervisor: He burst
through every record
during the fitness exam,
and he worked
with some class-s heroes
to destroy that meteor,
but because he came
out of nowhere,
people are saying he's a fraud.
Any other class-c hero,
I'd stop.
Worker: Let him go.
This may be our chance
to see how strong he really is.
Supervisor: Saitama,
here's the location.
Now head there immediately.
( Mumen rider panting )
( Growls )
( Yells )
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
Genos: Those of you
who can still walk,
leave the shelter now!
I cannot promise I will win.
Run while I keep him busy!
( Crowd gasping, yelling )
Deep sea king: Hmm?
None of you monkeys
will escape me!
¶¶
( Deep sea king screams )
Genos: Lightning eye!
Deep sea king: Huh? Oh?
Can't see.
Ohh!
Genos: Machine-gun blows!
Deep sea king: You do like
combo attacks, don't you?
( Crowd screams )
Deep sea king: Yaah!
Girl: I--i just know
you can do it!
Deep sea king: Quiet!
Now you melt, little girl.
( Genos gasping )
( Girl gasps )
( Metal clanks )
( Deep sea king chuckles )
( Roars )
If you'd focused on me...
You could have easily dodged
my little ball of acid.
Instead you chose to sacrifice
yourself to save a runt.
You're a fool,
but I give you credit
for giving me a few scratches.
Heh heh. Of course,
they've already healed.
Now die.
Mumen rider: Justice crash!
( Bicycle clatters )
Deep sea king: Huh?
( Thunder rumbling )
The cyclist for justice,
mumen rider is here!
Genos: The top hero in class c?
No. Do not--
man: It's mumen rider!
Man #2: Mumen rider's
come out here to save us.
Man #3: But he...
( Mumen rider yells )
Deep sea king:
I'm bored already.
Mumen rider: Haah!
( Grunting )
Deep sea king: Hmm?
( Mumen rider grunts )
Deep sea king: Oh.
Oh, apologies.
I nearly forgot to kill you.
Mumen rider: Justice tackle!
( Grunting )
Deep sea king: Huh?
Mumen rider:
No one expects much...
( Groans )
...not from me.
They think a class-c hero
won't be much help.
( Gasps )
I know that better than anyone!
I'm too weak for class b.
I'm not good enough.
I know that much.
I'm aware that I have
no chance of beating you.
No one needs to tell me
anything like that!
Deep sea king: What are you
babbling on and on about?
Begging for your life?
Mumen rider:
And yet, I must try.
( Genos gasping )
Mumen rider: It's not
about winning or losing!
It's about me...
Taking you on
right here and right now!
( Crowd gasping )
¶¶
deep sea king:
Enough of your rambling.
Time to finish you off.
( Mumen rider gasping )
Boy: You can do it!
Mumen rider, you can do it!
You're the cyclist for justice!
You can beat him!
Beat that weird monster!
Beat him!
I believe in you!
- Man #4: He's right! Get him!
- Woman: Yeah! Do it!
Man #5: We're all counting
on you, mumen rider!
- Man #6: Good luck!
- Man #7: Beat him!
Woman: You can do it!
( Mumen rider slaps helmet )
( Growls )
( Yelling )
( Music stops )
( Silence )
Deep sea king:
Pathetic waste of time.
Hmm?
( Mumen rider gags )
Saitama: Nice fight, man.
You should be proud of yourself.
Deep sea king: Hmm?
Yet another piece of garbage
washed up on my shore?
( Thunder rumbles )
Saitama: Huh?
Whoa! Hey, genos!
Are you...Still alive?
Genos: Mas...Ter.
( Saitama sighs )
Good. Hang on a second.
I've gotta pound this sea freak
or whatever it's called.
( Thunder crashing )
Deep sea king: I heard that!
¶¶
( sizzles )
Deep sea king: Hmm?
Impressive.
Still on your feet
after one of my punches.
Clearly you're different
from the rest of this trash.
Saitama: Huh? Your punch had
no power behind it. That's all.
Man #8: Hey,
someone else is over there.
Who is that? A hero?
Man #2: That head.
I saw him in the hero registry.
Man #3: I know him.
He's a class-c rookie, right?
I think he's rank two.
Man #9: Class c? For real?
Man #2: So we're still
gonna get killed.
Great. Perfect.
Woman #2: Yeah, but that punch
didn't hurt him at all.
Man #3: That's your imagination.
I mean, you saw how many heroes
were blown away
by that thing's punches, right?
Deep sea king:
King of the deep,
lord of the seas, that's me.
All life on earth
comes from the sea,
as if she were our mother.
In other words,
as ruler of the seas,
I am the absolute peak
of a pyramid
that includes every
living organism on this world!
Defying me means--
saitama: Yeah, yeah.
I got it. I got it.
It's raining out,
so let's get this over with.
( Deep sea king roars )
( Crowd gasping )
( Cheering )
- Man #4: Yeah!
- Woman #1: Thank goodness!
Boy: He did it!
Saitama: Well,
that was lame.
I kinda had my hopes up, too.
( Sonic panting )
Now I'm back with my weapons,
you monster. Heh.
Damn you, deep sea king.
You got away.
Saitama: Ohh.
What's that?
Genos: It is the mail.
The post office
cannot come here.
It is too dangerous,
so the drone
delivers the mail now.
Saitama: The post office
has a drone?
Genos: No. It is
the hero association's.
Saitama: Oh, I gotcha.
¶¶
genos: The public
sends these to the heroes.
You could say
they are like fan letters.
Saitama: Whoa. For real?
Are any of them for me?
Genos: Indeed.
Saitama: Coolness!
Why don't we go in
and open them!
( Twinkle )
Saitama: Hmm?
( Genos gasps )
Damn it.
I will find out
who sent it, master.
Saitama: Here's a guy
with free time.
( Crowd cheering )
Man #3: All it took
was one punch!
One punch! Just one!
Man #9: Is he really class c?
Man #2: No way!
- Man #10: Or maybe...
- Man #9: Huh?
Man #10:
It's because the monster
wasn't really all that tough.
Man #11: No way. You saw
how many heroes went down.
Man #10: Whatever. Just means
all those heroes
were a bunch of weaklings.
Man #11: Well, maybe.
When he took down that thing,
it didn't look that tough.
Man #10: After all,
a class-c hero
took it out
with a single punch.
What's that say
about the heroes it beat?
They may call themselves
class a or class s,
but it seems like their titles
don't mean a thing.
( Chuckles )
Man #12: Stop it!
Enough of that!
Those guys
risked their lives for us!
Man #10: Risked their lives?
Come on! Anyone can do that,
but a hero has to beat monsters.
Meh. Guess it all ended up well
this time, so whatever.
But I think it's more
than a little annoying
when people
who are really just average Joes
show up and try to save you.
If you're gonna
call yourself a hero--
man #13: Shut your fat mouth,
you smug punk!
Man #10: Relax!
Why are you getting mad at me?!
The hero association's funded
from our donations, right?
As long as we're
the ones paying for it,
those clowns
had better protect us.
The fact of the matter
is that bald guy pretty much
took care of it all by himself,
so in the end, all those
other guys died for nothing.
Anyone can come up with a way
to buy a little extra time.
When you get right down to it,
the other "heroes" didn't do
anything heroic at all.
Man #13: I said shut up!
Man #12: We were all saved.
Just leave it at that.
- Woman #2: Exactly!
- ( Saitama laughing )
( Laughing continues )
Today's my lucky day!
The other heroes
wore the monster down,
so beating it was child's play,
a piece of cake!
Good thing I was late.
I barely did anything, and now
I get to take all the credit.
Hey! Go spread the word
about this, all of you!
I'm the one who finished
the monster off! It was me!
If anyone says
the only reason I won
is because I got here late,
I'll kick your ass!
Man #14:
What's he talking about?
Man #15: The monster
was already weak?
Man #16: Huh?
Hang on. That's saitama!
Man #17: Saitama?
Man #16: Yeah. Heard of him?
He's the hero from city z
that everyone calls a cheat.
Man #17: What? A cheat?
Man #18: I know that guy.
He appeared out of nowhere
and climbed
up the ranks super fast.
Man #16: Yeah, pretty fishy.
Saitama: Hey, you guys,
gonna need you to look after
the fallen heroes, okay?
'Cause if they up and die on me,
how am I gonna cash in
on their work?
Man #9: Man, what a dirtbag.
Man #2: Whoa, he is a cheat.
Man #3: So he's
just taking the credit?
Man #9: Compared to him,
those other guys
seem a little more heroic.
Man #2:
Where would we be right now
if the other heroes
hadn't fought?
They saved us!
Man #3: Yeah, I feel so grateful
to every last one of them.
( Genos thinking )
Master saitama,
is this really what you want?
Saitama: Hey,
it stopped raining.
Genos: If this is the path
you choose to walk,
I promise I will not interfere.
But in the future,
if the day comes
that you are ever
caught out by this,
at that moment, I will--
saitama: Hey...
There's one more.
Hmm.
Someone's thanking me.
Genos: Then it must be
from somebody you saved, master.
Saitama: I see. Any left?
Genos: Oh, there is one
from the hero association.
Saitama: What? Really?
Are they firing me?
Fine. Let me see.
Wait. What's this?
I'm class c, rank one?
¶¶
so what's the deal?
Why'd you call me in?
Interviewer: When you listed
yourself with the hero registry,
you were given
the association handbook.
Interviewer #2:
Haven't you read it?
It clearly lists each one
of our rules and regulations.
Saitama: Yeah, I guess
I've got it somewhere.
Interviewer #1: No matter.
Congratulations on attaining
rank one in class c.
Saitama: Huh? Oh, I get it.
You guys decide the rankings.
It's all up to you, right?
Interviewer #1: Well,
there are actually more members
on the review board,
but the four of us here today
will be handling your interview.
Saitama: What interview?
Interviewer #1:
The top-ranking class-c hero
is given the opportunity
and option
to be promoted to class b.
However, if you wish
to remain in class c,
that's fine as well.
Interviewer #2:
How about it, Mr. Saitama?
Do you want to move up?
Although, if you do,
you'll be ranked
at the very bottom again.
Saitama: Well,
either way is fine,
but I suppose moving up
would be pretty cool.
That way, there'll be no more
of the weekly quota stuff.
And besides that,
I can't stick to class c forever
with genos in class s.
Interviewer #1: I see.
So you're wanting a promotion.
Interviewer #3:
First, we'll need you
to answer some questions
and undergo
a psychiatric analysis.
Executive: So that's saitama,
the one who finished off
the deep sea king. Hmm.
Executive #2: What do you think?
Some say he's a fraud.
Executive #1: He set new overall
records in the fitness exam,
so his physical ability
is far from fraudulent.
Executive #3: Interesting.
Well, if you want
to believe the rumor mill,
he cheated
on the written exams, too.
Worker: Rumors are just rumors.
It doesn't make much sense
to have any doubts
about him at this point.
The situation before us
is that he's wanting to move up.
For the time being,
why not let him do so?
If he's for real,
he'll make it in class b.
- Executive #2: Hmm.
- Executive #1: I see.
And if he's a fake, he'll
soon regret making that choice.
That young man is entering
a cruel and callous world.
Worker: When the time comes,
we'll know what to do.
Amai mask: Promotion to class b?
Heh. You really interrupted
my filming for this?
It's not something
that needs my attention.
Supervisor: I understand,
but this is a verdict
for the executive--
amai mask: Listen to me.
I don't want to be involved
in every decision,
just the ones regarding
heroes class a and above,
since they have
an impact on society.
As a hero in the same class,
if they're inadequate,
it ends up
hurting my image, too,
especially this last incident.
It was absolutely appalling.
Surely you must agree?
Supervisor:
Speaking of social impact,
the hero now wanting
to move up the ranks
is the very same man who
finished off the deep sea king.
Amai mask: Hmph.
( Ambulance siren wailing )
( Stinger growls )
( Lightning Max growls )
( Both sigh )
Puri-puri prisoner:
Why the sour pusses, kittens?
Both: Huh?
Puri-puri prisoner: It doesn't
show off those cute faces!
- Stinger: It's you!
- Lightning Max: No way!
I thought you were in prison!
Puri-puri prisoner:
I escaped just to see you two!
Now time for your angel shots!
( Both screaming )
Puri-puri prisoner:
Come back, you guys!
You need your injections!
Eh?
( Grunts )
( Footsteps )
Saitama: So I'm class b now.
All those tests
sure took long enough.
Meh, it's not like
I had to be somewhere.
Oh.
Something smells good.
Owner: Welcome.
( Bubbling )
Saitama:
The house special, please.
Owner: You got it.
Mumen rider: Care for a drink?
Saitama: Huh?
Mumen rider:
If you're not drinking,
let me buy your food.
Saitama: What for?
- Mumen rider: Heh. For that.
- Saitama: Huh?
Mumen rider: You were
at the association.
Think we should celebrate
your promotion.
¶¶
saitama: Thanks.
I appreciate the ride.
Should I walk?
Mumen rider: No, it's okay.
I can handle it just fine.
Hey, are you scared?
- Saitama: Hmm?
- Mumen rider: You got separated
from your friend, didn't you,
genos, class s?
Saitama: Mm-hmm.
Mumen rider: The enemy
is threat level demon,
a monster so formidable
that even if all
the s-class and b-class heroes
ganged up on him,
they'd still lose,
so if you wanna run...
Saitama: Are you class s, too?
Mumen rider: No, I'm class c.
It's all right. Go ahead,
and laugh if you want to.
Saitama: Why would I
laugh at that?
It's pretty tough
having to try and make
those weekly quotas
for us class cs, isn't it?
( Mumen rider chuckles )
You're a pretty funny guy.
You know that?
Saitama: Hmm?
Mumen rider:
The name's mumen rider,
and I'm a hero, like you.
( Saitama chuckles )
Uh, hey! Watch it!
Oh! You're that guy!
Mumen rider: I've been
on the lookout for you.
I couldn't say everything
in my letter.
( Saitama chuckles )
I see.
Maybe some mozuku then?
Mumen rider: Hey,
give us your best mozuku!
Owner: Comin' right up.
¶¶
( Singing in Japanese )
( Woman wailing )
¶¶
it's coming, coming!
Assistant: Madame shibabawa,
what is it? What's wrong?
Shibabawa: A violent catastrophe
looms over our future!
Assistant: Madame shibabawa,
get a hold of yourself!
Please, you--
shibabawa: This is the end!
I've seen it!
( Gasps )
The--the earth is doomed!
( Groans )