¶¶
saitama: It's been five days
since I debuted
as a professional hero.
There haven't been
any serious incidents so far.
However, in the midst
of this new beginning,
genos ended up
staying at my house.
So, uh, what are you
writing over there?
Genos: I'm recording the details
of your lessons
and training regimen.
( Saitama thinking ) Crap.
He's raising the bar again.
I can't think of a single thing
I could possibly
teach this guy.
I feel bad, like i'm
scamming him or something.
Come on. Think.
Just make up some techniques
or a spiritual theory
or something!
Ahh! Strength training
is all I've got!
I know genos won't be
satisfied with that!
- Plus the dude's a cyborg!
- Genos: By the way...
Saitama: Huh?
Genos: Earlier, at the seminar,
they said
if you are a class-c hero
and you have
no activity for a week,
your name will be removed
from the hero registry.
Will you be all right, master?
( Saitama gasps )
Seriously?! They said that?!
Genos: Yes.
Saitama: But I was watching TV,
and there wasn't
anything to act on.
Genos: The news only reports
major incidents,
like natural disasters,
terrorism,
and dangerous monsters.
You always battle
the most powerful enemies,
so you were probably
not aware of this,
but class-c heroes mostly
take care of purse snatchers,
robberies, and random attacks.
With class c so full of heroes,
they must actively look
for cases to survive.
Many get discouraged
and change careers.
Much in the same way
a salesman makes cold calls,
nothing will come your way
without legwork.
Saitama: This is no time
to be reading manga!
- Genos: Are we leaving?
- Saitama: I am!
You stay here! Don't you get it?
If I'm with
a class-s hero like you,
- then I won't get any credit!
- Genos: But as your disciple--
saitama: Genos,
from the very beginning,
my intense desire to be a hero
was what led me down
the path of strength training.
That's how I made it this far.
For you,
perhaps things will change
if you aim higher as a hero,
to be more
than what you are now.
Frankly speaking,
you're a cyborg,
so training your body
would be useless.
Instead, a change in mindset may
lead you to greater strength.
( Thinking )
Damn, listen to me.
I'm just making
all this crap up.
( Aloud )
So in other words,
it's not about having
raw power or technique.
Not at all.
It's about training your mind.
You must first fight your way
through
the professional hero industry.
Aim to break into the top 10
of the class-s heroes.
That will be your goal
for the time being.
¶¶
genos: I understand.
I will try!
Saitama: He totally bought it.
Sweetness.
¶¶
( woman yelps )
Saitama: After that,
I sped around town
while frantically looking
for bad guys.
I ran...
And ran...
But...
The city was completely quiet!
( Cat meows )
Saitama: I give up.
( Panting )
Just one more day left.
Guess I'll just head home, then.
( Dog barking )
Saitama: I'll leave tomorrow's
problems to tomorrow's me.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Saitama shuddering )
It's quiet out here today, too.
There's nothing to do! Nothing!
I'm gonna lose my registration.
Huh?
Uh...
¶¶
hold up!
I've run into you before!
What was your name again?
Seed-on-the-ground.
No, wait. Lost-and-found?
( Gasps )
Jack-o-lantern panic!
Sonic:
No, it's speed-o'-sound Sonic.
I've finally found you,
saitama.
Today is the day we settle our--
saitama: Hey, sorry. I'm busy.
See you around, okay?
Sonic: Huh?
Insolent worm!
Think you can run from me?!
What the--
I didn't even see what happened.
His face should have
been sliced open,
but the blade was--
saitama: I told you...
I'm busy.
Plus I'm pissed,
so anyone in my way...
Gets punched.
( Sonic gasps )
Woman: That's the guy.
He's very, very dangerous,
a public nuisance.
Please stop him.
Hero: Is that so?!
You're the offender, huh?!
Well,
the tank-top tiger is here!
( Saitama thinking )
A hero?
( Laughs aloud )
Bad news, Sonic.
They think you're
some sort of criminal.
Maybe getting tossed in a cell
will cool off
that hot hea--hmm?
Tank-top tiger:
She means you, cue ball.
Saitama: Huh?
Woman: He's been running
all around town
with this scary look on his face
since yesterday morning.
Saitama: Hey, wait a minute!
I'm a hero, too!
Tank-top tiger:
You are, huh?
I've never heard
of a hero like you.
Saitama: So what?
I just started, okay?!
Tank-top tiger: In any case,
you're causing problems
around here for everyone.
If you're really a hero,
then don't go around
frightening people.
You're hurting all
the other heroes' reputations.
Man: Hey, isn't that
tank-top tiger over there?
Man #2: Can't believe it!
- It is tank-top tiger!
- Woman #2: No way!
Man #3: Awesome!
He's the real deal.
( Tank-top tiger chuckles )
Even class-c heroes
get recognized,
well, if they're
in the top 10, anyway.
So, how 'bout it, new guy?
You wanna fight and make me
look good in the process?
Sonic: Exploding shuriken.
( Tank-top tiger screams )
( Woman #3 screams )
Man #4: Tank-top tiger!
Man #5: Is this
really happening?
Saitama: What was
all that for, Sonic?
Sonic: He was interfering,
so I tucked him in for a nap.
Man #6: Hey, call a hero!
Now! Quick!
Man #7: Run for it!
Sonic: Interesting, though.
So you, too, have become
one of these worthless
association heroes?
Then all I have to do
is to create a situation
where you're forced to fight,
saitama the hero!
Hail of carnage!
Saitama: Hmph.
( People screaming )
Saitama: Hey, stop it!
Sonic: Saitama,
come forth, and fight me!
You're a hero!
Can you prevent their deaths?!
( Explosion )
Boy: Dad. ( Crying )
Saitama: Ugh, damn it all.
Can't everybody
just let me do my job?
I don't have time for this crap.
I gotta find a bad guy
to take down.
( Shuriken whooshing )
Hmm?
( Sonic laughs )
Saitama: A bad guy...
Sonic: Not coming?
Then I'll go to you!
Saitama: I'm right here.
( Sonic sputtering )
Saitama: Huh.
I wonder if taking out
this guy'll count as work.
Man: The man apprehended by
the class-c hero the other day
in city z is suspected
of being involved
in several heinous crimes,
including assassination.
( Supervisor sighs )
City z again, huh?
What's the status of
the investigation I requested?
Woman: You mean the one
for the ghost town?
- Supervisor: Yes.
- Woman: Let me see.
It appears an official inquiry
has been submitted.
- Supervisor: Hmm.
- Woman #2: Well,
doesn't that sound
ever so interesting?
Want me to check it out?
Supervisor: T-tornado?
- Now, how did you get in here?
- Tornado: Why?
- Aren't I allowed in here?
- Supervisor: Of course.
For city z,
the investigation's a formality.
It's not worth your time.
Tornado: What?
You mean you don't think
I'm good enough?
( Supervisor gasping )
Woman: That's not it.
The association decided
this was not a class-s matter.
That's all.
Supervisor: Yes, exactly right.
Tornado: Hmm.
Humph.
You'd better tell me
if you find anything
that looks like it can fight.
It'd be so much faster
if I went myself.
You guys are idiots.
( Supervisor sighs )
Man: Reports have come in
from each location
being investigated.
First is watchdog man,
class-s hero,
investigating city q.
"Nothing unusual."
- Man #2: Nothing unusual?
- Man #1: Yes, sir.
Man #2: That's hard to believe.
We all know city q is a hot zone
with more casualties
and monsters
than any other area
under our jurisdiction.
Man #1: Well, sir, knowing him,
I'm confident
he's implying that.
It says, "whatever occurs,
I'll be able to take care of it
on my own, without assistance."
Though he's focused
his efforts on city q,
his track record at monster
elimination is top-notch.
There's really no need to worry.
Man #3: Class-s heroes
don't pay attention to details.
They're not ones
for writing reports.
Man #1: Next, city w.
Class-a hero heavy Kong
reports, "nothing unusual."
In city h, mushroom, class b,
and horsebone, class c,
report, "nothing unusual."
In city d, lightning genji,
class a, reports,
"slow restoration
after the devastation caused
by the gigantic creature aside,
nothing unusual."
Woman: Cities b and d
both sustained extensive damage.
The association
took a lot of heat for that.
Man #1: In order to prevent
more disasters from occurring,
we must be diligent
and uncover any covert activity
that could threaten
our society.
Man #4: Well, keep in mind
this investigation
was requested
for that express purpose,
but detecting these monsters
is more difficult than expected.
Man #1: City f, class-a hero
snakebite snek reports,
"hammerhead, former leader of
the paradiser terrorist group,
has been spotted
in a suit and tie."
Hammerhead:
I'm really impressed...
Man #1: "Further investigation
is being conducted."
No other reports.
Man #2: What about city z?
I've heard repeated rumblings
of a potential disaster
brewing somewhere
in the abandoned area.
Man #5: No reports available.
However, two highly capable
class-a heroes
have been sent to investigate,
so we should get to the bottom
of these rumors soon.
Hero: Here we are in city z.
Are you ready to begin
our little inquiry?
Golden ball:
Yeah, let's get on with it
and get outta here.
Spring mustachio:
City z is quite expansive,
but further ahead
lies the abandoned area,
the one we were told
to investigate.
Compared with other areas,
city z
has an abnormally high rate
of monster-related incidents.
The frequency
has been increasing
over the past 10 years,
the last few
having more and more advanced
monsters appearing,
and the residents have fled for
the safety of the city center.
Golden ball:
Yeah, I know all that.
This place is
like a real ghost town,
only the water and electricity
are still intact, right?
Spring mustachio: Indeed.
Looking for a cheap house?
Golden ball: Heh. Come off it.
People say something
real nasty's living round here.
I'm sure even you
must have heard about it.
Spring mustachio:
But of course.
I assume
that's why the two of us
have been assigned
to this investigation.
Golden ball:
Once we hit the abandoned area,
we're gonna need to walk in
with our game faces on.
Spring mustachio: Agreed.
We mustn't let our guard down
for a second.
Golden ball: But why here?
Why an increase in monsters
in this place?
Spring mustachio: Well,
that's the mystery, isn't it?
There are quite a few theories
out there about it,
and here's mine.
A colony of monsters
resides here
and is naturally producing
more of them,
or perhaps a queen exists,
birthing more of her kind.
Hmm.
¶¶
of course,
I have no proof of this yet,
but there is something
to this ghost town,
or rather, something in it.
Of that, you can be sure.
( Beeping )
Genos: Proximity alarm.
What tripped it?
Golden ball: If we can hunt down
this mysterious being,
the two of us'll go straight
to the top of the rankings.
- No doubt.
- Spring mustachio: True.
We can't let Mr. Amai mask
remain first forever, can--
both: Something's there!
Golden ball: Was that a monster?
Spring mustachio:
There's no way to be sure,
but it's rather hard
to imagine a human still living
in these conditions.
Let's pursue it!
Genos: It seems
they are not after us.
Monster: Can this be
the place I heard about?
I don't know.
Sure don't seem like it.
Aw, man!
I came all this way for nothing.
Isn't anyone around?
Spring mustachio: A monster.
It came out of nowhere.
Let's take it down!
Ready, golden ball?
Golden ball: Hell, yeah.
- Victory to the swift!
- Monster: Hey! People!
Golden ball: I can blast through
a 20-millimeter steel plate
with one of my shape-memory
golden bullets!
Suck on this!
¶¶
( gasps )
He just flicked it away.
( Screams )
( Sputters, gags )
Spring mustachio: Golden ball!
( Yelling )
Hmm.
Monster: Wow!
Hmm?
Spring mustachio: Tomboy...
Thrust!
( Monster gasps )
Spring mustachio: It slipped
past my tomboy attack.
Monster: Not too bad.
Spring mustachio:
Those tentacles,
from the way they react,
they're tough as steel.
A monster that can use
its infinite number of tentacles
like steel whips.
Such power.
( Sighs )
I must call in reinforcements
from the association.
I would like to ask you
a question, if I may.
I was just wondering if you
were born in this neighborhood.
Monster: Hmm? Nah.
Actually I'm from out of town.
I heard a bunch
of crazy-strong monsters
were all getting together
around here.
Too bad. Looks like it
turned out to be just a rumor.
But now...
I feel like it'd be kinda fun
to stick around
and make the rumor true,
a self-fulfilling prophecy.
I could be
"the ghost town monster."
It's got a nice ring to it!
Woman: We have
a request for backup
from the two heroes that were
dispatched over to city z.
Class a, rank 29, golden ball
has been knocked out.
Class a, rank 33,
spring mustachio is in trouble.
They're in the abandoned city.
Supervisor: Call in
all nearby heroes
for immediate assistance,
class a and above.
Hero: See the monster alert
for city z?
Hero #2: The threat level
seems to be tiger or higher.
Hero #3: Is it
the ghost town monster?
Hero #4: They're not sure yet.
Hero #5: I'll go.
I wanna catch the tiger
by its tail.
( Spring mustachio panting )
( Laughs )
Now I understand.
If it means running into
monsters like this all the time,
I wouldn't want to live
around here either.
( Groans )
( Sword clatters )
Monster: Ugh. Boring!
Come on! Seriously?
I finally kick a hero's butt,
and I don't even get
a single scream.
Now that I think about it,
even if I start living here,
I'll never be famous
if there's no people around.
Guess I'll just keep going.
Gotta find out
where they're living.
( Gasps )
There's somebody.
Is it another hero?
Hmm? Or just a dude?
I thought all
the regular humans cleared out.
If the monster really did exist,
there's no way
he could live here.
I guess that means
it was just a rumor.
Saitama: Crap.
I forgot to buy
konbu soup stock.
( Door opens )
Genos: Master, I saw a lot of
konbu right outside the door.
Saitama: Oh, yeah.
Funny story. I, uh...
Just happened...
To catch it...
For a really good price.
Genos: People say that konbu
is good for growing hair,
but there is
no scientific proof,
so its real benefits
have yet to be confirmed.
I did some research,
so I am sure, master.
For example,
according to this site--
saitama: No one said
anything about hair!
Man #1: City z
investigative report.
"There is nothing
noteworthy to report
"in the downtown
or residential areas.
"During our investigation,
we encountered
"a ferocious monster
in the abandoned area,
"but were unable
to exterminate it
"and left it in defeat.
"Fortunately, we escaped death,
"but the monster we
encountered there disappeared,
"and it's possible
that it still roams the area.
"Also, according
to the monster itself,
there's a rumor
that powerful..."
Man #2: "...Monsters
have gathered in secret
and already exist in this area."
That's rough.
It sounds like it was
a pretty brutal encounter.
Woman: A monster, huh?
Man #2: Eh, yes.
( Woman sighs )
Think I'll pass this time.
Tornado: You see?
I told you I should've gone!
You're so lame!
Supervisor: I'm sorry,
but when faced
with something like this,
I'm sure even you
would have had a tough time.
It's unprecedented.
Tornado: Hmph!
( Supervisor gasps )
Tornado: You idiot.
I would have been just fine.
Man #1: The rumor
has not been confirmed yet,
but the reinforcements saw signs
that point to the existence
of some horrible monstrosity.
Hero: Holy crap,
what happened out here?
What kind of monster
could cause such violence?
I'd hate to face off against
whatever this crazy thing is.
Hero #2: Hmm? What's this?
Is it a part of the monster
spring mustachio's
been fighting against?
Hero #3: There may have been
a territorial dispute
between the monsters.
But either way,
seems like there's
definitely something here.
Man #1:
This requires resolution.
We must continue
our investigation
and maintain vigilance
over city z.
¶¶
man #3: Hey,
did you hear the news?
There are monsters living
in the city z ghost town.
Man #4: Yeah.
I heard someone say
the toughest ones
are secretly plotting something.
Monster: No, no. Not that rumor.
It's about
a more dangerous monster.
Monster #2: What do ya mean?
Monster #3: You didn't hear?
I'm told the place
has now become terrifying
for both humans and monsters.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
Genos: Master, I filled in
the holes in front of the house.
Saitama: Ah. 'Kay, thanks.
Genos: Also, your rank has
gone from last place, 388th,
to 342nd. Congratulations.
Saitama: Oh? Wait.
'Cause of that panic guy?
Guess he boosted my ranking.
Cool.
So I think it's been
about a week now.
Have you done anything?
Genos: No. Not yet, anyway.
Saitama: Well,
you've still got time, I guess.
Genos: I am still ranked last
in class s for ability,
17th place.
Saitama: Heh. Sounds like
you still need lots of training.
Genos: But according
to popularity rankings
voted on by the public,
I am number six.
Saitama: Why?!
Genos: "A 19-year old genius
who made his debut in class s."
"He is fantastic."
"He is so handsome."
"Love how he refuses to do
media interviews. Cool."
- Those kinds of comments.
- Saitama: Good god.
How are you not embarrassed
to read those out loud?
Genos: Quite simple.
This is based on impressions
from my photo.
They are not
true evaluations of me.
I think nothing of them.
Saitama: Oh? Yeah?
Genos: "The cyborg prince."
"Behind the steely exterior,
I feel his fragile self."
"Top five handsomest heroes."
Saitama: Enough already!