¶¶
man: It's decided.
Mumen rider will remain
the top-ranked class-c hero.
Man #2: Understood. I will
inform him of our decision.
Man #3: It's baffling.
I don't know why
he has no desire
to move up to class b.
Man #1: Our next item
on the agenda for this meeting,
the 55th hero certification exam
and the circumstances
surrounding it.
Currently, the total number
of candidates is...
Woman: Over 11,000,
with the exam offered
at six different venues.
That's an increase of more
than 22% over the previous exam.
( Men gasp )
Man #3: We mustn't be happy
with simple quantity.
Even with more candidates,
if the quality
of the heroes is reduced,
then the numbers
are meaningless.
Therefore, we must be even more
critical during evaluations.
Also, it's my understanding
that a certain
person of interest
is taking the exam this time.
Man #4: Yes, sir.
It hasn't been confirmed yet,
but I'm confident that his
participation will indeed occur.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
( overlapping chatter )
Worker: Candidates, please form
two lines for registration,
each line single file.
Thank you!
( Applicants laugh )
Examiner: Next, side-to-side
jumps for 30 seconds!
Ready.
Go!
( Applicants gasp )
Examiner: Next,
the 1,500-meter run.
Go!
( All gasp )
Examiner: Next, weight lifting!
( Applicants gasp )
Examiner: Next, shot-put!
( Judge gasps )
Examiner: Vertical jumping!
( Judges gasp )
Examiner: Whac-a-mole!
Punching machine!
( Applicant gasps )
Applicant #2: I'm leaving.
¶¶
( overlapping chatter )
( Saitama sighs ) Finally.
I'm done with all the tests.
Now I just wait
for the results.
Uh, hey. Are you done, too?
Genos: Yes.
Saitama: Say, uh,
what's the point in you
taking fitness tests?
Genos: Huh?
Saitama: Well, I mean,
can't you just give them
the data on your specs
or something?
Genos: Uh...
Saitama: Never mind.
So, how did it go?
Genos: The challenges
were far too simple,
both the written
and fitness exams.
Saitama: I know, right? Heh.
Is that really all there is
to becoming a hero?
Genos: We should get
our results soon.
70 points is a passing grade.
Heh. The written test
was so easy,
anyone could get
full points on it.
That just leaves
the fitness test,
which, for us, poses no problem.
I got 100 points.
Saitama: Seriously?
Genos: Yes. Hmm.
It says that I am now fully
certified as a class-s hero.
Saitama: Class s?
What's that mean?
Genos: When it comes down to it,
I am sure these rankings
mean very little.
So how did you do?
Saitama: Huh? Hmm.
Oh! The letter says I'm also...
Genos: Class s.
I am not surprised.
Saitama: Huh?
Genos: On top of that,
the font size
is bigger than mine.
( Saitama chuckles )
Genos: Just as I expected.
By the way, what did they
ask you at the interview?
Saitama: The interview?
Genos: Yes.
Interviewer: All right, then,
just one final question, genos.
Does this building
look familiar to you?
We've been
secretly investigating
a group of troublemakers.
These ne'er-do-Wells
call themselves
the house of evolution.
Just when we identified
their center of operations,
we found
the building in question
had been
mysteriously destroyed.
Interviewer #2: Obliterated
by intense firepower.
Interviewer #1: Are you...
Responsible for this?
Genos: Actually, I am.
( Interviewers gasp )
( Interviewer #3 gasps )
( Grunts )
Genos: Ah, I see.
I suppose that since they found
your performance satisfactory,
no interview was needed.
Master?
Saitama: Maybe,
or it's because
I'm a class-c hero
with a score of 71 points.
Maybe that?
( Genos gasps ) I see.
Viewing only part
of the document, I mistakenly
thought the top half of the "c"
was an "s."
Saitama:
Stop analyzing it, jerk!
Genos: It must be a mistake.
I will speak to the person
in charge about this.
Saitama: No, don't!
You'll just embarrass me!
( P.A. chime rings )
Man: Mr. Genos, Mr. Saitama,
there will be a seminar
for successful candidates
at 4:00 P.M.
Please come
to lecture hall number three.
Saitama: All right then.
Come on.
When you get right down to it,
only thing that really matters
is we passed.
Let's get this over with
and go home.
Man: We finally found
the cyborg
we've been looking for.
Man #2: Yeah? So I've heard.
Man #1: In consideration
of his past accomplishments,
we've made an exception and
certified him as a class-s hero.
I just wanted to make sure
you were notified
of this recent turn of events.
Man #2: Yes, and I approve.
Hmm.
Genos, huh?
Lecturer:
Congratulations on passing.
( Saitama chewing gum )
Lecturer: Now, to be honest,
one of you only made it
on a fluke,
so unless you want
your luck to go to waste,
I'd better see you
giving it your all.
And don't get cocky. Got it?
Keep your certified hero status
in mind.
From here on,
I expect you to act modestly.
After all,
your faces'll be placed
on the main page
of the hero association website.
( Growls ) Did you hear me?
That goofball head
on your shoulders
is gonna be shown
to the whole world.
If you don't want
to humiliate yourselves...
Hyah! ( Yelling )
...aspire to be
a distinguished hero like me.
Genos: Master!
Lecturer: As a class-a hero,
I have influence over
the association's decisions,
so those
who behave irresponsibly
will lose their points
and get demoted!
Have I made myself clear?
( Saitama thinking ) What should
I have for dinner tonight?
¶¶
genos: Apparently
the hero association
was formed
about three years ago.
Saitama: Oh. Huh.
So they're relatively new.
Genos: A monster
attacked the grandchild
of some millionaire named agoni.
The child was saved
by someone passing by.
When agoni heard what happened,
he created this system
and used his fortune to
establish the hero association.
The rest is history.
Saitama: Well, they have
some pretty boring seminars.
Genos: In any case,
as new heroes,
we will be known
around the world.
We will be respected
and compensated.
From now on, we can work
with our heads held high.
Master.
Saitama: Huh?
Genos: Now I am
officially your disciple.
Saitama: Uh...
Genos: Please, continue to teach
and guide me as my mentor.
Saitama: Sure.
Genos: All right, then.
Good night, master.
Saitama: Y-yeah. See you later.
Crap.
Maybe I shouldn't have
been so quick
to say I'd take someone on
as a disciple,
especially this guy.
Lecturer:
Those two newcomers today,
did they really pass the exam?
Their attitudes were awful.
I'm class a,
rank 38, damn it.
They hadn't the slightest idea
who I was.
Plus they have no clue
how the world works.
They're a couple of amateurs.
They'll be dead in no time.
- Interviewer: No.
- Lecturer: Huh?
Interviewer:
Genos got perfect scores
on both the written
and physical exams.
He's a phenomenal rookie
who gained a class-s ranking
right off the bat.
The other new recruit, saitama,
had terrible scores
on the essay,
but got a perfect 50
on the physical.
That score was how
he was able to pass at all.
In practically every activity
on the fitness exam,
he broke the hero association's
test records
by inconceivable margins.
Frankly, it's as if there's
a god residing in that body.
Snek, you've already
been outranked by genos.
His s-class status
reflects that.
And with
his physical test score,
saitama might soon
catch up to you.
Snek: That jackass?
Saitama: If I get
to the top of class c,
then I'll get promoted
to class b,
and class a is above that,
with class s
being even above that.
I guess genos is
actually pretty amazing.
I don't know.
Maybe this isn't the kind
of hero I wanted to be.
- ( Running footsteps )
- Huh?
Snek: The newcomer seminar
isn't over yet!
In this business,
there's a little thing
we like to call
rookie crushing.
A lot of us established heroes
hate the prospect
of being outranked,
so we crush newbies...
With moves like this!
- ( Groaning )
- ( Bird squawking )
( Wind blowing )
Saitama: Hero registry?
Genos: Yes, I am a class-s hero,
and you are a class-c hero,
both ranked last in our classes.
Right now, we are still listed
under the designations
of genos and saitama,
but as we perform
more heroic acts,
we will acquire hero names.
Saitama: Hold on. "Hero names"?
What are those?
Genos: Well, I believe
they are considered to be
like nicknames based
on a hero's characteristics.
For example, I might be
the blonde cyborg.
Saitama: Wait.
If that's how it works,
I could end up
with a really sucky name,
like the caped baldy.
Genos: Huh.
You can be ranked by ability,
but you can also
be ranked by popularity.
There are some heroes
that have fan clubs.
( Saitama gasps )
Genos: But no one really cares
about that stuff.
Saitama: Wha?!
Genos: Master, thank you
for agreeing to my odd request.
I appreciate it.
Saitama: No problem.
I mean, I did promise
to make you my disciple and all.
Is right here good?
Genos: Perfect!
Saitama: So we're just having
a practice bout, right,
not fighting for real?
Genos: That is
what I had in mind, yes,
but I want you
to go all out.
In return, I, too, will give it
everything I have got.
¶¶
please, master.
( Saitama gasps )
Oh.
Oh, man.
That was close.
Could've burned my clothes.
( Genos gasps )
Damn.
I need more speed!
Saitama: Hmm?
( Genos grunts )
( Beeping )
There.
Saitama: Oh.
Genos: Incinerate.
I got him this time.
Master will have to take me
more seriously now.
What the?!
Saitama: It looks like I win.
Whoa. Nyah.
- Genos: Master.
- Saitama: Yeah?
Genos: You still remember
the rules of the bout, right?
You are supposed to evade
any attack
you are able to dodge.
Take it seriously,
and no fooling around.
Do not hold back,
and lastly...
Keep fighting until I am
no longer able to fight.
Even master saitama
cannot explain it,
the secret
to his incredible power.
This fight may finally
give me some insight.
You are to show me no mercy.
Now then, again!
( Gasps )
No way.
Saitama: Come on. I'm hungry.
Time for lunch.
Let's grab some udon noodles.
Genos: Unbelievable.
I am fully prepared
to do anything
in order to become stronger,
but I cannot picture myself
ever approaching
master's power...
Not even close.
He is on a different level.
Saitama: What's the matter?
You don't like udon?
Man: I see.
That's his location?
Thanks. I'll head there now.
No. Don't worry about a thing.
I'm just gonna let him know what
the industry's expecting of him.
Saitama: I'm glad you like udon.
I love it.
Genos: Yes. Although,
I am not a picky eater.
Saitama: Well, to be honest,
I'm also kinda low
on funds right now. Oh?
Hey, how 'bout
another match, genos?
Genos: Hmm?
Girl: Look at them!
That's insane!
Girl #2: No way!
Woman: My goodness,
what a handsome man.
( Saitama groans )
I give.
( Genos slurps )
( Gasps )
So, do I win?
( All gasp )
Saitama: Holy crap.
You're awesome.
Genos: Hmm?
Owner: Welcome. Sit anywhere--
( diners gasp )
Man: You must be genos.
- Saitama: Huh?
- Genos: Hmm?
Amai mask: I'm amai mask,
class a, rank one.
I'd like to talk to you.
Saitama: Class a, rank one?
Girl #1: It's amai mask.
- Girl #2: He's so gorgeous.
- ( Woman swoons )
Genos: Talk? About what?
Saitama: He might be
another rookie crusher.
Be careful, genos.
Genos: I see.
Wait here, master.
I shall return.
Very well.
I was considering a walk
to digest my food.
( Amai mask chuckles )
Heard you were certified class s
by special exception.
Genos: True, and what of it?
Amai mask: Hmm.
( Saitama chewing ice )
Wonder if he's doing
all right out there.
- ( Clatter )
- Eh?
Ohh.
So, are you finished already?
Genos: Yes.
Saitama: You really
are a class-s,
to have
the top-ranked class-a hero
come to personally crush you.
- Genos: No.
- Saitama: Hmm?
You're saying
he wasn't here to fight?
Then why was he here?
Genos: Well,
from the sound of it,
he came to welcome me.
Saitama: Wait. What?
What's that mean?
- Girl #1: Excuse me!
- Both: Huh?
Girl #1: Sorry,
but you're friends
with amai mask, aren't you?
May I shake your hand?
( Squeals )
Thank you very much!
Girl #2: Shake mine, too!
( Woman swoons )
¶¶
saitama: Class-s heroes
and class-c heroes
sure get treated differently.
If you think about it, though,
isn't that kind of
like fraud money?
I mean, you're a cyborg, right?
Genos: Yes.
Saitama: Never mind.
Anyway, now we have one win
and one loss between us.
Starting today, we're certified,
professional heroes.
Let's do our very best, okay?
Genos: Right.
Amai mask: Listen to me.
A professional hero
must always be
a beautiful symbol of justice.
That is my philosophy,
especially if you're class s.
( Genos grunts )
Amai mask: Come on.
There's no need to glare at me.
I came all the way here
just to see you.
How was the certification exam?
Genos: It was utter garbage.
Such exams are a waste of time.
( Amai mask gasps )
( Chuckles )
Genos: If you came here
to fight, get on with it.
This, too, is a waste of time.
Being hot-blooded is fine,
but if you take it too far...
You get burned.
I'll forget about your criticism
of the association.
Thank you for your time.
We expect great things from you.
Welcome to the team...
Genos.
Genos: Master.
Saitama: Huh?
Excuse me. I will be back.
Saitama: Oh.
Sure. Okay.
See you later.
Genos: Yes. Good-bye.
¶¶
Amai mask: A waste of time, huh?
Humph.
What an interesting fellow
you are.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
Saitama: So, uh,
when you said, "back,"
you meant later tonight?
Genos: Yes. I needed some time
to go home
and gather up my things.
May I live here with you now?
Saitama: No way. Absolutely not.
Genos: I have rent money.
Saitama: Did you
bring a toothbrush?
Genos: Yes!