¶¶
storyteller: Long ago,
there existed
a brilliant young scientist.
Through the musings
of his astonishing genius,
he was able to make a number
of significant contributions
to human knowledge.
Eventually, however,
his accomplishments
led him to be disillusioned
with the world.
Though he was constantly
showered with praise
for the intricacies
and revolutionary creations
of his mind,
none of his ideas or theories
ever received
even the slightest bit
of support
from the scientific community.
Rather than advancing
human civilization,
his goal was
the artificial evolution
of humans as a species.
That was the only dream
he had ever had,
but not a single person
came forward
to help him achieve his vision.
Dr. Genus:
Damn these simple apes!
"Dangerous ideas"?
Treating me like a freak?!
( Scoffs ) Do these
lowbrow simians really think
humans have come this far
by avoiding risks?
Idiots who think that mankind
no longer has the need to evolve
have no right
to call themselves scientists,
let alone pass on their genes.
Of course,
this plan and its fruition
were always for my sake.
I will carry it out,
even if I must do it all myself.
Storyteller:
He devoted himself to research,
but it was only
after he turned 70
that his efforts yielded
the results
he'd been searching for.
( Dr. Genus gasps )
Storyteller: First,
the scientist regained
the prime age-range
of his youth.
Next, he began
cloning himself en masse.
He named his laboratory
the house of evolution,
and with his clones,
he conducted countless
experiments with animals,
creating new life
and new species.
His experiments then shifted
to human subjects.
Saitama: This is
taking too long!
Armored gorilla: Huh?
Saitama: What's this
got to do with me?
You're just tryin'
to sound cool again.
( Armored gorilla sighs )
Saitama: Enough jibber-jabber.
Just get to the point, okay?
Genos: My master
is a very busy man.
Summarize it all
in 20 words or less.
Armored gorilla: Uh...
Sure. Sorry about that.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
armored gorilla:
So, in other words, uh,
the boss man has become
passionately curious
about you and your body.
Saitama: Too bad.
I'm not interested in dudes.
Genos: Master,
that is not what he meant.
Your body surpasses
normal human limitations,
so he plans on using it
for his research on evolution.
Unless he is stopped, I am
sure he will try this again.
We cannot allow him
a free hand.
Our move should be
to attack him.
Saitama: Sure. Let's go.
Genos: Right.
( Footsteps )
Huh?
Now?!
Saitama: Yeah.
There's a sale on tomorrow.
Can't do it then.
Genos: But, master!
Armored gorilla:
This doesn't sound good.
Better tell the doctor.
Genos: Hey, you.
( Armored gorilla yelps ) Yes?
Genos: I have one last question.
The house of evolution's
cyborg development,
did it begin
over four years ago?
How many were created?
Have any of them destroyed towns
in the past?
Armored gorilla: Um,
I'm not really sure,
but at the house of evolution,
I'm the only combat cyborg.
Genos: Hmm.
Dr. Genus: Impossible!
Our elite force,
formed for the destruction
of these archaic humans,
wiped out?!
Clone #33: According
to armored gorilla's report,
the two responsible for doing so
are on their way here now.
( Dr. Genus gasps )
Second clone: If they manage
to make it to the lab,
all of our research, everything
that we've been working on,
could be destroyed.
Clone #78:
We're in serious trouble.
( Dr. Genus sputters )
We're forced to use
our trump card.
( Clones gasping )
Dr. Genus: Begin preparations
for the release
of carnage kabuto.
Clone #50: No way!
Fifth clone: No, not him!
Sixth clone: What?!
That's crazy!
Seventh clone:
He'll finally be released?
Eighth clone: He's right.
That might be the only way.
- Maybe we should stop him.
- This is too dangerous!
- There is no turning back now.
- There's no other way!
Dr. Genus: Quiet down.
He'll be our very last resort.
Clone #33: But, sir...
Dr. Genus: We'll start
by activating all our traps
from the first floor
to the eighth.
If we're lucky, they will
take care of the intruders.
I'm aware of what will happen
to us should we fail,
especially to me.
( Bird trills )
Genos: I did not think we
would be running the whole way.
Saitama: How else
are we gonna get there?
Genos: It was my assumption
that you had the ability to fly.
Saitama: You know humans
can't do that, right?
Genos: It is amazing
that you are never late.
You are a true hero.
Saitama: Really? You're kidding.
I hardly ever arrive on time.
Genos: We're here.
This is the place
we were told about.
Saitama: So this is...
Genos: The house of evolution.
Saitama: One, two, three,
four, five, six.
Looks like it's
about eight stories high.
Uh...
That seemed a little rash.
Don't you think?
Genos: You see,
in the interest of efficiency,
I thought it would be best
to destroy them all
in one fell swoop.
Saitama: Well,
that was efficient, but...
We could have at least seen
what our enemies
had in store for us.
You didn't really
think that one through.
Looks like there's a basement.
( Clone yells )
( Clone panting )
Stop it! Just stay away!
( Carnage kabuto growls )
Dr. Genus: Hey, uh,
carnage kabuto,
tell me,
are you feeling all right?
It would appear you've killed
a bunch of my clones again.
Are you satisfied?
Carnage kabuto: Eh?
You fool!
Why would I be satisfied, huh?
I've been kept locked up
deep beneath the earth.
I'm the strongest warrior in
the entire house of evolution!
Dr. Genus: You were imprisoned,
because you're
mentally unstable.
We couldn't control you.
There was no choice
in the matter.
Carnage kabuto:
You couldn't control me?
( Laughs ) Moron!
I am the ultimate culmination
of the "new human"
you guys have sought
for so long.
My intelligence
and physical strength
are incomparable to your own.
The way I see it,
you and all of your clones
should be the ones obeying me.
( Slurps )
( Dr. Genus thinking )
No, you're a failure.
It's true you perform
at unheard of levels,
but you lack humanity.
( Aloud ) Go ahead
and kill me if you want.
Plenty of clones
could take my place.
Carnage kabuto: Oh?
Dr. Genus: But I have
a favor to ask first.
There's a specimen
I simply must have.
He's proven to be
extremely strong.
Only you could defeat him.
I want you
to catch him for me...
( Carnage kabuto chuckles )
Dr. Genus: Dead or alive.
( Footsteps )
Saitama: This basement is huge.
I'm getting kinda fired up.
( Genos gasps )
Saitama: Huh?
Genos: I sense living beings
deeper inside.
Master, two of them
are approaching us.
Saitama: Hmm?
( Glass shattering )
Carnage kabuto: Yeah!
Here we go!
Which one is it?!
Dr. Genus: The one...
On the right.
Carnage kabuto: In that case,
you don't need
the one on the left!
Saitama: Genos?
Oh.
Whoa.
Carnage kabuto:
My name is carnage kabuto.
We've got a combat
experimentation room
back this way.
Let's throw down in there.
( Chuckles )
Saitama: You just turned genos
into a piece of bad modern art.
Let's do this.
( Carnage kabuto chuckles )
¶¶
pretty big, huh?
It's the largest room
in this facility.
This is where we fight
to test our combat abilities,
which means there's plenty
of room here to kick your ass.
Well, then,
let's start the killing.
Hmm?
Ah. Still alive, are you?
( Genos gasps )
¶¶
You fool!
Genos: Machine-gun blows.
He got me good.
Let me...
( Carnage kabuto chuckles )
Genos: Take him.
Saitama: Your face is cracked,
and you're all smashed up.
Don't push yourself.
( Genos gasps )
With his breath?
Impossible!
Saitama: Genos.
Hey, are you all right?
Genos: Yes, master.
Saitama: No, you're not!
Look at your head!
( Carnage kabuto laughs )
( Babbles )
Saitama: Well, I've gotta admit
that was pretty impressive.
You've gone
and gotten my hopes up.
( Dr. Genus gasping )
I have always been critical
of humans
and their inferior abilities.
Aside from myself,
the entire species can
only be viewed as dumb animals.
That realization
was agony for me.
If memory serves,
I was 15 years old at the time.
That's when I hit upon my plan
to evolve the human animal
and create a world
where I could live contentedly,
a utopia of my very own,
created by my genius,
a realm populated
by a new human breed
transcending humanity,
bringing about
a new world order.
( Gasping )
I must see it through.
Compared to the horrible anguish
I endured back then,
this physical pain I feel now
is nothing.
Carnage kabuto:
What's the holdup?
Let's get this thing going.
Bring everything you've got.
Dr. Genus: Carnage kabuto,
the strongest
and most brutal creation
of the house of evolution.
Let's see how your archaic human
processes fare against a monster
that is the apex
of artificial evolution.
Or will you and this challenge
reveal new avenues
for experimentation?
I can't wait to find out.
( Boot squeaks )
Carnage kabuto: Oh, I see it.
I see it!
You're supposed to be strong.
Saitama:
Don't disappoint me now.
You're supposed to be
the ultimate weapon
in this place, right?
Clearly, you're not the same
as those guys this morning.
Look at you,
just oozing with confidence.
( Carnage kabuto laughs )
Genos: Such speed.
( Carnage kabuto gasps )
Saitama: What are you doing?
Hey.
Dr. Genus: Absurd!
Carnage kabuto retreating?!
Carnage kabuto:
If I'd attacked him just now,
- he would have killed me.
- ( Heart beating )
Who the hell is this guy?
He's leaving himself wide open,
yet all of my instincts
are screaming,
sending out danger signals!
Saitama: Huh?
Carnage kabuto: Bastard!
What are you,
some kind of freak?!
How in the hell
did you get that strong?!
( Genos gasps )
( Carnage kabuto panting )
Saitama:
So you wanna know as well?
Okay, fine.
¶¶
genos, you listen
carefully, too.
Genos: Wait. You mean he is
going to tell us right now,
the secret to his amazing power?
Dr. Genus:
I want to know as well.
Saitama: Huh? Who are you?
Dr. Genus: I am genus.
Saitama: Huh?
Fine. Whatever. Listen up.
Genos: No, it is too risky.
He must not let them
know his secret.
Saitama: First,
what's important
is to make sure you really stick
to this intense
training regimen.
Dr. Genus: Wait a minute.
Not modification surgery
or genetic enhancement?
Just training?
Carnage kabuto: What training?
Saitama: Listen, genos.
You have to keep doing it...
No matter
how difficult it gets.
It took me a full three years
to get this strong.
100 push-ups...
100 sit-ups...
And 100 squats...
Then a 10-kilometer run!
Do it every single day!
( Saitama panting )
And of course, make sure
you eat three meals daily.
Just a banana
in the morning is fine.
But never, ever use the
air conditioner in the summer
or heat in the winter,
so you can strengthen the mind.
In the beginning,
you'll wish you were dead.
You might start thinking,
"what's the harm
of taking a day off?"
But for me,
in order to be a strong hero,
even if I was spitting blood,
I never stopped.
I toughed it out
and endured the pain.
I did squats even when my legs
felt like they couldn't move.
Even when my arms started
making weird clicking noises,
I kept doing push-ups.
( Growling )
A year and a half later,
I started to notice
a difference.
I was bald...
And I had become stronger!
In other words,
you gotta train like hell
to the point
where your hair falls out.
That's the only way
to become truly strong.
Guys fooling around
with this "new human race"
and evolution junk,
they're never
gonna make it this far.
Human beings are strong,
'cause we can change ourselves!
Dr. Genus: W-what did he say?!
Carnage kabuto:
Is this guy for real?
Genos: Master...
You are so...
Full of crap!
Saitama: Huh?
Genos: That is nothing more
than standard strength training!
And it is really
not even that intense!
It is just a normal level!
I--i have to get stronger!
Understand me?!
I cannot believe
you would do this!
I did not ask to study
under you to hear jokes!
Master saitama, please.
Your power is more than one
could achieve by just training.
Dr. Genus: Yes, that's right.
I want to know your--
genos: Your true secret,
please reveal it!
Saitama: Look, genos,
you may not believe me,
but that's really all I did.
( Genos gasps )
Carnage kabuto: Oh, yeah?
Dr. Genus: No! Don't do it!
You mustn't!
Carnage kabuto: If you don't
wanna tell us your secret,
so be it.
Dr. Genus: Oh, my god.
Looks like he's going
on another rampage!
Carnage kabuto: I bet
you aren't stronger than me!
- Not even close!
- ( Alarm blaring )
( Whirring )
Carnage kabuto: But since you
seriously pissed me off--
( growls )
I'm gonna annihilate you.
Carnage mode!
¶¶
when I get like this,
I lose control for a whole week,
and my lust for death
cannot be quelled!
After I kill you,
I'll head into town.
Once I'm there, I'll go
on a bloody killing rampage
until next Saturday!
If you really are a strong hero,
then try and stop me!
( Roars )
¶¶
saitama: No way. It can't be.
Genos: Master?!
Saitama: Damn it.
I may have inadvertently
made a horrible mistake.
This guy's in carnage mode,
and he said he'll be
on a rampage for a whole week?
Carnage kabuto: Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die!
Saitama: So he'd be like
this through next Saturday,
one whole week from today.
"Next Saturday."
In other words, he's saying
today is Saturday, too.
That means...
Dr. Genus: It's all over.
There's no one in this world who
can stop my glorious creation.
Saitama: That means...
Today is...
Bargain day at the supermarket!
¶¶
( screams )
Dr. Genus: Who the hell
is this guy?
Saitama: I screwed up!
Dr. Genus:
What is he talking about?
Genos: I believe...
He is upset
because he is missing this.
Master, the store
closes at 10:00 P.M.
That is about
four hours from now.
If we really hurry,
we can still make it.
Saitama: Wait. So you're saying
there's still a chance?
Genos: Right.
- Saitama: Let's go, genos!
- Genos: Yes, master!
Dr. Genus: I think I'm finished
dabbling with evolution.
( Rumble )
It would appear...
I'm the one who must change.
( Sniffs )
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
Man: Yes, the on-site
investigation is under way.
Yes, that's correct.
Like the other cases,
the area has been thoroughly
burnt by intense flames.
Everything we've seen
points to the young cyborg
as the one who's responsible.
Yes. Got it.
Look at this.
Such devastating power.
Man #2: Yeah.