Newscaster:
What could be the cause
of the massive mosquito outbreak
plaguing our nation this year?
We'll ask Mr. Kafetch,
a mosquito expert
who has written
several books on the subject.
Kafetch: Thank you
for having me.
These mosquitoes belong
to an entirely new species.
Therefore, I honestly
know nothing about them.
Newscaster: Ah, come on!
What good are you?!
Get him off my show!
( Clears throat )
I mean, how interesting.
Let's take a look at our map...
Saitama: Man, city z's
right in their path.
Now we've got a mosquito plague
to deal with?
Newscaster:
We interrupt this program
with a breaking news bulletin.
A large swarm of mosquitoes
has been sighted in city z.
Mummified remains
of attacked farm animals
have also been found.
If you encounter
a large swarm of mosquitoes,
it is strongly suggested
that you flee immediately.
- ( Buzzing )
- Saitama: Uh...
( Buzzing )
( Sirens blaring )
( Mosquitoes buzzing )
¶¶
( sirens continue )
Announcer: This is
an emergency evacuation warning.
Threat level: Demon.
No resident is to go outside
under any circumstances.
Please remain indoors.
I repeat, no city z resident
is to go outside.
Man: Acquiring target.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Glass shatters )
( Looter laughs )
Thanks to that warning,
they're all empty.
Like someone's actually
gonna die from a mosquito bite.
Heh.
What's losing a little blood
if I get to walk away
with all of this?
Was that the wind?
( Gasping )
What the--
( yelling )
( Monster sighs )
( Slurps )
( Moans )
( Groans ) Come on.
That wasn't nearly enough blood
to satisfy my needs.
Now go get some more for me.
Huh?
Cyborg:
Target has been acquired.
Monster: Hmm?
Cyborg: I see. You make
the mosquitoes suck the blood
and then take it all
for yourself.
You must be controlling each one
by using some sort of signal.
That would explain
their mysterious behavior.
So if I were to get rid of you,
their leader,
would the swarm disperse
as well?
( Monster chuckles )
Our next meal is here.
Go drain that fool dry.
¶¶
cyborg: Incinerate.
( Monster gasps )
Cyborg: I will eliminate you.
Stay right where you are.
( Monster gasps )
( Giggles )
You believe
that you can eliminate me?
( Giggles )
Then go on and try!
Saitama: I got you.
( Buzzing )
( Sputtering )
Damn mosquitoes.
¶¶
( Monster chuckles )
Cyborg: Incinerate.
( Monster giggles )
Maybe a leg next time.
( Gasps ) Huh?!
What the--
what happened to my legs?
( Gasps )
Hmph!
Cyborg: Futile.
You cannot escape from me.
Monster: What the hell
is that guy?
He'll get me if I
don't come up with something.
( Chuckles )
The townspeople may be hiding,
but there are plenty
of animals around to feed on.
That's it.
Come here, little ones.
Empty all the delicious juices
you carry into me!
¶¶
cyborg: So many.
If she has been collecting blood
from the whole town
as well the surrounding area,
then it may be more than
a simple food source for her.
I should put an end to this
as soon as I can.
Saitama: Get back here, damn it!
You and I aren't done yet,
you little bastard!
Cyborg: Who is this idiot?
Saitama: It's in my mouth.
( Spitting )
Nasty little--huh?
What's that swirling?
Are those mosquitoes?!
( Gasps )
- Cyborg: You there...
- Saitama: Eh?
Cyborg: Evacuate.
That swarm is conscious,
and if it senses you,
it will attack.
Saitama: Seriously?
That's bad news. We should get--
( monster laughs )
Saitama: Oh.
¶¶
( Music ends )
Cyborg: Since she could speak,
I thought she would have
at least
human-level intelligence,
but in the end,
she was just a bug.
Bringing the mosquitoes together
made for one
easy-to-burn swarm.
When I first spotted her,
I confirmed that there
were no living beings
within 500 meters
in all directions,
so this location
allowed me to fire at will.
Wait a second. That guy might--
saitama: Man, you saved me.
You're pretty amazing,
aren't you?
You could say you totally
made the bugs bug outta here.
( Imitates drum sting )
( Cyborg gasps )
Saitama: Oh. See,
that was a joke about
the mosquitoes being bugs.
( Monster laughs )
You idiot.
I no longer need
my tiny, little helpers.
I mean...
( Cyborg gasps )
Monster: Just look
at how strong I've become!
( Laughs )
¶¶
Can't your macho punches
kill a little mosquito?
( Laughs )
What a weakling.
Cyborg: I get it now.
The more blood
she is able to consume,
the more powerful she becomes.
Monster: I think
I'll have your head next!
Cyborg: I let my guard down.
I have no chance of winning.
All I can do is self-destruct.
Forgive me, doctor.
( Monster laughs )
( Music stops )
( Cyborg gasps )
Saitama: Bugs, they suck.
Cyborg: Wait a minute!
Saitama: Hmm?
Cyborg: Please,
tell me your name!
Saitama: Oh. It's saitama.
Cyborg: I would like
to be your disciple.
Saitama: Um, sure.
Uh...
Hold on. What?
( Cyborg breathes deeply )
Sensei, sir!
( Footsteps )
Saitama: You actually showed up.
Uh...
Genos: Genos, sensei, sir.
Saitama: Could you lay off
all the "sensei" stuff?
Genos: Yes, master!
Saitama: Not "master" either!
¶¶
have your drink, and go home.
I'm not looking for disciples.
Wait. You're back in one piece?
Genos: Indeed. My body
is mostly mechanical,
so my parts can be replaced.
Saitama: You're an odd one,
aren't you?
Genos: What kind of parts
have you installed
on your body, master?
Saitama: Don't use any.
Genos: But what about the
skin-colored armor on your head?
Saitama: Yeah,
that's just my skin, dude.
Genos: That's odd.
You appear far too young
to already be bald.
Saitama: So I'm bald?!
What's your problem, huh?!
Genos: My problems?
You are asking me
to list each one of them?
Saitama: Yeah, no, thanks.
I'm good.
Genos: Four years ago,
when I was 15,
I was still a real human being.
Saitama: You heard me say,
"no, thanks," didn't you?
Genos: Though we were poor
and had to pinch pennies,
we were still able to get by.
We lived a peaceful
and happy life together
until that fateful day
when a crazy cyborg
went out of control
and attacked our town.
We never knew why it happened.
Most likely,
a failed body modification
generated an irregularity
in his brain.
He destroyed
everything in sight,
parks, schools,
buildings, my house.
He even took the lives
of everyone in my family.
Miraculously, I survived,
but being
only a weak 15-year-old,
I was alone and at the end
of my strength in a ruined town.
That's when Dr. Kuseno
happened to pass through.
The doctor,
a scientist for justice,
was on a mission
to stop the rampaging cyborg
and end his oppression.
I asked the doctor to give me
body modification surgery
to make me better,
stronger, faster.
That's how I was reborn as
a cyborg who fights for justice.
I promised Dr. Kuseno I would
terminate the evil cyborg
and return peace to this world.
Saitama: Huh, I see--oh.
Genos: It's been
four years since that day.
At 19 years old,
I'm focused and driven.
I wander from town to town
eliminating evil.
The monsters
and criminal organizations
I have destroyed are numerous,
but I have been unable
to locate any clues
about the insane cyborg
and have become
increasingly frustrated
and restless.
I find myself chasing
a virtual image of that cyborg
whenever I face my enemies.
Then last week, when
that mosquito monster appeared,
I let my concentration slip
and paid the price.
I thought I could lose to no one
but the rampaging cyborg,
so I neglected to analyze
the data on my opponent
and rushed in headlong
to confront her.
- The result, as you know...
- ( Bird flaps )
Was that an enemy with
immense strength bested me.
If you had not been in the area,
master saitama,
I would have
undoubtedly been destroyed.
Master, you saved
my life that day.
The life that was once saved
by Dr. Kuseno many years ago
has now been saved yet again
by you, master saitama,
and I feel the weight
of that responsibility.
I must not allow myself to die
before finding and destroying
that cyborg once and for all,
and to achieve that,
I have to continue
fighting evil
as a righteous soldier
until that fateful day comes
when he appears before me.
I need to get stronger.
Last week, when I saw
what your punch was capable of,
I knew immediately
that I had to study
under you as your disciple.
If only I could be
as strong as you have become.
Such awesome power.
I have an old enemy
who must be defeated
at all cost,
though the battle
is not for me alone.
It is for my entire hometown
and for Dr. Kuseno as well.
I fully realize
I am still inexperienced,
but now, more than ever before,
I need incredible strength
so that I can eradicate
the greatest of evils.
- Dr. Kuseno is a man who--
- saitama: Enough, you idiot!
Shorten this stupid story
to 20 words or less!
Man: Mosquito girl
was defeated in battle?
And with one punch, you say?
Oh, well.
She was little more than
a prototype unit, after all.
Why is he naked?
Man #2: Unknown.
Man #1: Well, whatever.
I'm sure he'll make
quite an excellent specimen.
We shall study his physiology,
by force if necessary.
Send a messenger,
and invite him here,
to this,
our "house of evolution."
( Chuckles )
Genos: Here is
the short version,
as requested, master.
Please teach me the way
to become strong like you are.
I beg of you.
Saitama: Hey, genos...
Genos: Yes?
Saitama: How old are you again?
Genos: 19, sir.
Saitama: So young.
I'm sure you'll surpass me
in no time.
Genos: Do you really mean that?
Saitama: I'm 25 years old now,
but I didn't even begin training
'til I was 22.
( Genos gasps )
Saitama: Fine, I'll teach you,
but it won't be easy.
Sure you can you handle it?
¶¶
genos: Yes, sir!
( Beeping )
High-speed object approaching.
It is here.
Saitama: Huh?
( Monster shrieks )
( Laughs )
Greetings! I am--huh?
Saitama: You're gonna pay
for my ceiling.
Slug monster: So...
Frog monster: Huh?
Slug monster:
It seems our advance agent,
kamakyuri, is down.
I can't sense him
with my telepathy.
Frog monster: What? Wait a sec.
Wasn't he one
of our stronger guys?
Genos: Two more outside.
Master, leave them to me.
Saitama:
Don't bust people's ceilings.
Genos: Oh. Never mind, then.
Saitama: Enough, okay?
There's a front door
for a reason.
Oh.
Ah.
Genos: Master!
Saitama: No, it's cool.
I'm fine.
I kinda feel like
a young bamboo shoot.
( Monster #4 robotic voice )
Elevated energy level detected.
¶¶
( genos gasps )
A cyborg?
Could it be...
Cyborg: You are not the target.
Saitama: Hey, what's going on?
I can't see.
Cyborg: Out of the way!
Genos: Now listen.
I have a few questions for you.
( Cyborg growls )
Saitama: Hmm?
- ( Monster #5 laughs )
- Saitama: Huh?
You appear to be
in what they call a tight spot.
Magnificent work, ground dragon.
Ground dragon:
It complicates things
if they put up a fight.
Genos: Master!
Cyborg: You dare look away?
Quite courageous!
¶¶
( Music stops )
Cyborg: I am the pinnacle
of the house of evolution's
science.
I am armored gorilla.
Your attacks have no effect.
Genos: The house of evolution?
What does it want
with my master?
Armored gorilla:
That is none of your business.
And it is our rule
that any who oppose us
be eliminated without exception.
Therefore,
you will now be destroyed.
¶¶
lion monster: Hey, jerk-off,
what's with
that stupid look? Huh?
( Saitama yawns )
Being underground
keeps you cool,
but at the same time,
it's nice and warm.
- ( Lion monster growls )
- Saitama: I'm sleepy.
- Could you get lost?
- ( Lion monster scoffs )
( Laughs )
It would appear that I need
to teach you your place.
Listen up! I'm gonna slice
your eyes out with these.
Then we'll see if you're
still such a smart-ass!
And just so you know,
the beast king never
lets anyone off easy.
( Ground dragon gasps )
Saitama: Well,
enough fooling around then.
Listen up. This is your
only chance to apologize.
You clumsy oafs
smashed up my ceiling.
Beast king: Heh.
Well, is that so?
Then prepare to witness
the true power
- of the mighty beast--huh?
- Saitama: Aw, man.
I got dirt
in my special pants place.
Beast king:
Hey, are you even listening?
Saitama: Let me
just shake this out.
Beast king: You done yet?
Saitama: One sec.
Okay, I'm done.
Beast king: Then once again,
prepare yourself
to witness the true power
of the almighty beast king!
¶¶
lion slash!
Slug monster:
Are you okay, frog man?
Beast king:
Outta my way, pissants!
( Laughs )
Such is the law of the jungle,
and you're next!
( Roars )
Ground dragon:
No, wait! Don't kill him yet!
Beast king: Lion slash!
Meteor power shower!
( Yelling )
¶¶
Saitama: Consecutive...
Normal punches.
( Ground dragon gasps )
Saitama: Oh.
Ground dragon: No one told me
he'd be that strong.
It's best we retreat now
and regroup.
( Yelps )
Saitama: Found you.
Ground dragon: No! Impossible!
( Rumble )
Saitama: Huh?
Genos: You will answer
the question,
or you are going to be
eliminated. Your choice.
Armored gorilla: It is you
who will be eliminated,
you blithering fool.
I am the third
most powerful fighter
in the house of evolution.
At your power level, you will
never beat the beast king,
the second
most powerful fighter.
You will be destroyed.
Saitama: Is this
the guy you mean?
Genos: I believe it is.
( Armored gorilla sighs )
( Normal )
Hey, look, I'm sorry!
I'll tell you everything!
Just don't kill me!
Saitama: Wait. What happened
to your high-tech robot voice?
Armored gorilla:
Sorry about that.
I was just
trying to sound cool.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
man: What do you mean?
Man #2:
Are you sure about this?
Man #3: The hit team
wiped out?
- Man #4: Confirm it.
- Man #5: What's the conclusion?
( Overlapping chatter )
- Man #6: It may be a mistake.
- Man #7: What's going on?
Dr. Genus:
What's all the commotion?
( Men stammering )