[PLISETSKY FANGIRLS squealing]
[FANGIRL 8A]
Look!
[FANGIRL 8B]
Yakov and his team are here!
[FANGIRL 8C]
Yurochka!
[FANGIRL 8D]
Yuri!
Mira, watch my luggage.
Huh?
Hey, Coach Yakov.
Yuri ran off somewhere.
Da.
He has family here in Moscow.
They're picking him up.
[PLISETSKY]
My name is Yuri Plisetski.
My goal is to be named
the top skater in the world
in my first senior season.
I am the unbeatable
Ice Tiger of Russia.
Oh, Yuri!
Grandpa!
[crack]
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY groans]
[PLISETSKY]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I forgot about your bad back!
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY] I made
my pirozhkis for you--eat!
Hey, Grandpa. Ever try
a pork cutlet bowl?
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY]
What's that?
[PLISETSKY]
Something I had back in Japan.
They're really good.
So, my pirozhkis aren't
good enough for you now?
No! Sorry! That's
not what I meant!
[RADIO HOST 8A] Russian
national hero Victor Nikiforov
has returned home for the Figure
Skating Grand Prix series.
This year, he'll be coaching
rather than competing.
[YURI]
"Yuri vs. Yuri. The Horror!!
Rostelecom Cup, Short Program."
[REPORTER 8A]
How do you feel about
coming back to Russia?
[REPORTER 8B]
When will you return to skating?
Until the Grand Prix
Final is done,
I won't comment
on any future plans.
Right now, I see a lot of
potential in Yuri Katsuki.
I think the focus
should be on him
during the Rostelecom Cup.
[PLISETSKY]
I'm in it, too, stupid.
You're well-known as a skater
who likes a challenge.
Wouldn't you rather face
a man of Yuri's charisma
as a fellow competitor?
[PLISETSKY]
Hm.
Hey! It's Yurio!
[REPORTER 8D]
Yuri Plisetsky!
Did you all check out
the short program I designed?
For Yurio?
You're not Russia's
top skater anymore, Victor.
I'm the star of this event.
[YURI] Oh, it's
Seung Gil Lee from Korea.
I was on friendly terms
with the other skaters
at the Cup of China.
But here, not so much.
[MICHELE] You want to
date my little sister,
you better be ready
to go through me.
[laughs] Take it easy.
Mickey! Calm down.
We were just going
out to grab a bite.
[MICHELE]
My sister's out of your league!
You don't deserve to eat
at the same table as her!
Hey, Yuri!
We're just grabbing some food.
Would you like to come?
[SEUNG GIL]
No.
Jeez.
If you don't want to go,
maybe you could find a way
to say that without being
a total jerk about it.
I get no benefit
from being nice to you,
so why bother?
--[SARA] Seriously?
--How dare you
--speak that way to her?
I'll rip your eyeballs out,
you little runt!
I mean it! Get over here!
[SEUNG GIL]
You're in my way.
[MICHELE]
What?!
[gasps]
Why are you sneaking around?
[YURI] Hey, Yurio.
Good to see you again.
I know both of us can't win,
but I'm sure we'll
both skate well.
Niet .
You will suffer a miserable
defeat here in Moscow.
Then you will go back home
and Victor will stay in Russia.
[YURI]
What if he's right?
If I don't rank higher
than fourth here,
I won't advance to
the Grand Prix final.
And if I don't,
what will Victor do then?
[NAOHIKO]
The Men's singles short program
is about to start
here in Moscow.
Here's where the rankings stand
after the series' fifth event,
Trophée de France.
Only the top
six skaters
will advance to
the Grand Prix Final.
There are just two
confirmed qualifiers so far.
Otabek Altin of Kazakhstan,
who placed second
in Skate America and
won the NHK Trophy.
And Christophe Giacometti,
who placed third
at the Cup of China and first
at the Trophée de France.
And now the skaters
fighting for the
last four spots.
Canada's Jean-Jaques Leroy,
the lead contender
after winning on his home
turf at Skate Canada.
Seung Gil Lee
of Korea, a newcomer
to the Grand Prix Series
who placed second
at the NHK Trophy.
Michele Crispino of Italy,
here with his sister Sara,
after placing third
in the NHK Trophy.
Emil Nekola, from the
Czech Republic,
who took third at Skate Canada.
Russia's own Yuri Plisetsky,
who made a brilliant
senior debut,
finishing second
at Skate Canada.
And finally,
Japan's Yuri Katsuki,
who placed second
at the Cup of China.
He will be skating
in the final group.
The Rostelecom Cup results
will also determine
whether Thailand's
Phichit Chulanont
will advance to the Final.
Damn it, the livestream
keeps cutting out.
I knew I should've
gone to Russia!
That's it, you three,
get to bed!
--No You can't make us!
--[LUTZ] We wanna watch it live!
--[LOOP] Please, Mom!
[MOROOKA] All right, Group One's
six-minute warm-up has ended.
[SEUNG GIL'S COACH] Seung Gil,
are you listening to me?
Everything you do
is for PyeongChang.
That's where your focus
needs to be. Seung Gil!
[MOROOKA] Seung Gil Lee
of Korea, age 20.
In his first event,
the NHK Trophy,
he thrilled the crowd
with his short program
skated to this
piece, "Almavivo."
["Almavivo" plays]
[MOROOKA]
His first jump will be a quad.
He is the only
skater in the world
to have landed this
jump in competition.
A quadruple loop!
Incredible!
[SEUNG GIL]
The base value is 12.0.
[MOROOKA] Seung Gil Lee
has selected "greed"
as his theme for this season.
He hopes to gain an edge
in the competition
by amping up the sex appeal
in his performance.
Crap. He's doing that, too?
Sex appeal inflation!
[LOOP]
There is way...
[LUTZ]
...too much...
[AXEL]
...sex appeal!
[AUDIENCE applauding]
[MOROOKA] Seung Gil always
seeks to break new ground.
In addition to the exceptionally
difficult quadruple loop,
he also requested to skate
a mambo for his short program.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
Oh, he takes a fall!
[SEUNG GIL]
Enough rotation.
Second-half jump
gets a 1.1 multiplier.
So, 9.35 with a
deduction of one.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Triple Lutz, triple toe loop!
[MOROOKA]
No mistakes there!
[SEUNG GIL] Eleven point one one
points, with the multiplier.
Now the last element,
a step sequence.
[MOROOKA]
What a passionate step sequence!
The polish in his execution
should be well received
by the judges.
Zero expression,
but his steps are killer.
He's even better than
at the NHK Trophy.
[LOOP]
Totally!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[EMIL] Oh! That'll be
a hard act to follow, ya?
--I've never seen you get
--[SARA] I could devour him!
nervous before, and I don't
think you're going to start now.
You know, you're right.
We'll all make it to Barcelona!
[MOROOKA] Seung Gil Lee
scores 91.83, a personal best.
He's currently in first place.
Next up is Emil Nekola
of the Czech Republic, age 18.
[EMIL]
Hm!
I don't let crowd's response
affect my performance.
--[AUDIENCE cheers]
--Huh?
[MICHELE] There's no denying
that guy can jump,
but his performance
is lackluster.
Si .
[SARA]
Once Mickey's done,
it'll almost be time
for Group Two.
Did you hear that, Yuri?
Emil landed a quadruple
loop, as well.
We should clap for him, eh?
Oh. Sorry, I didn't catch that.
[JEAN-JACQUES] You did the same
jump at last year's exhibition,
didn't you, Victor?
I'd love to see that again.
I don't recall.
Aw!
[MOROOKA]
Emil Nekola's score is 82.43.
That means he is currently
in second place.
Hey, Mickey, let's
see you beat that!
Mickey! Sara! Hey!
[MOROOKA] Next up is
Michele Crispino of Italy.
His sister Sara
is here to support him.
[MOROOKA]
He is skating to "L'Homme Armé"
from the movie
Destiny of Knights .
[MICHELE]
Watch me, Sara!
I am your knight
in shining armor!
["L'Homme Armé" playing]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
Bravo!
[MICHELE] I've defeated
every man who has tried
to take Sara from my side.
She and I will be
together forever,
supporting each other
on and off the ice.
No one could love
her more than I do!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quad Sal.
[MOROOKA]
Ah, he fell!
[gasps]
[MICHELE] Sara, your own
short program is coming up.
I don't want you
to go into it worried.
As your older brother and a man,
it's my duty to protect you.
Unlike physical love, the love
of a brother is unconditional.
I will always be there for you!
[MOROOKA]
Next up is a triple Lutz,
triple toe loop combination.
[gasps]
[SARA]
Is he...?
[MOROOKA] He turned it into
a triple Lutz, triple loop!
A very high-difficulty
combination.
Among active skaters,
the only one to even attempt
it is his sister, Sara.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Well, that sure was a surprise!
[MICHELE]
Sara.
I'm sure you'll land that
combination, just like I did.
Don't worry. We will
always be together.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[SARA] He has to find a way
to skate without me by his side.
[MICHELE]
Sara!
[SARA]
Well done!
[SARA] If something doesn't
change, it will ruin both of us.
[MOROOKA] Michele Crispino's
score is 89.65.
He is currently in second place.
Grandpa, where are you?
[panting]
[MINAKO]
Oh, come on!
Are you kidding me, here?
Why can't they just show
the damn thing on live TV?
[MINAKO] There we go!
Wow, he's already up?
[ALL]
Go get 'em, Yuri!
I thought I told you
three to go to bed!
[MOROOKA] Yuri Katsuki
channeled the power of love
to take second
at the Cup of China.
I wonder what he's got
up his sleeve today.
[VICTOR]
Ah--
[YURI] The performance has
already started, Victor.
[VICTOR]
I know it has.
I'm going to go out there,
and I'm going to show my love
to the whole of Russia.
[ANNOUNCER 8B] The next skater,
representing Japan,
Yuri Katsuki!
[YURI]
That was so embarrassing.
I can't let the crowd intimidate
me in enemy territory.
I have to intimidate them.
["On Love: Eros" plays]
[JUDGES gasp]
["On Love: Eros" continues]
[MOROOKA]
Japan's Yuri Katsuki, age 23,
skating to "On Love: Eros."
He's been consistently beating
his short program
personal bests.
He will need to finish
fourth or higher here
to advance to the
Grand Prix Final.
[YURI] If I don't do well enough
at the Rostelecom Cup,
this may be the last time
I skate this program
with Victor as my coach.
I don't know how many
people in the world
want me to win. Probably
no one here in Russia.
It's not a very
comforting thought.
But that doesn't matter.
I can't let it stop me.
[VICTOR]
Yuri seems to be more motivated
competing further from home.
Whatever the reason,
he's in top form.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[MOROOKA] His first planned
jump is a triple axel
from a spread eagle.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
Very clean!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Salchow.
Yuri! That was amazing!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Quadruple
toe loop, triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA] He nailed the
jump combination, too!
[PLISETSKY]
His program has come a long way
since the "Hot Springs
on Ice" event.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[MOROOKA] Another flawless
performance on the heels
of his last short program
at the Cup of China!
It sounds like the crowd
is impressed, too!
Yuri!
[panting]
[YURI]
All right.
It looks like I got
my message across.
[PLISETSKY]
Damn it.
I thought, with Grandpa
here, I would be able
to skate agape perfectly.
Yuri! That was perfec--
Huh?
[YURI gasps]
Out of my way, piggy.
Well. I think he's
found... his agape.
[BOTH]
Finally!
Yurochka!
We love you!
Stay calm.
The crowd expects a lot,
but don't let them rattle you.
[LILIA] All the work you did
in practice won't betray you.
[muffled] Have confidence,
like any other...
[PLISETSKY] That's weird.
Everything sounds fuzzy.
Calm down, calm down.
--[AUDIENCE cheering]
--[PLISETSKY gasps]
[YURI]
[MOROOKA]
One oh nine point nine seven!
He beat his personal best again!
That puts him in first place!
[MOROOKA] Nikiforov is
so overcome with pride,
he kisses Katsuki's skate.
Now there's a devoted coach!
Davai ! Yurio!
Huh?
[YURI]
Skate well! Ganbate !
[PLISETSKY growls]
[ANNOUNCER 8B] The next skater,
representing Russia,
--Yuri Plisetsky.
--Yuri!
[MOROOKA]
The Russian skating prodigy,
Yuri Plisetsky, age 15.
His program was choreographed
by Victor Nikiforov.
[PLISETSKY]
Damn it.
I don't need you idiots
cheering me on.
I'm not that desperate.
["On Love: Agape" plays]
[MOROOKA] He's skating
to "On Love: Agape,"
a different arrangement
of the music
used in Katsuki's program
with an opposing theme.
Crap! I'm not
feeling agape at all.
I'm just angry!
[MOROOKA] Here comes his
first jump, a triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
Oh! he fell!
[PLISETSKY]
Damn it!
I haven't missed that jump
once in the last year!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A flying sit spin.
His position is quite beautiful.
[PLISETSKY]
It's not fair!
I've been pouring my
blood, sweat, and tears
into this since that
humiliation in Japan.
[PLISETSKY] I just lack
experience, that's all.
[MOROOKA] His first quad is
coming as part of a combination.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Quadruple Salchow.
Triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA] Fantastic execution!
Great height and flow!
It's hard to believe
he only started doing
that combination this season!
Now here comes his final jump.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
What a beautiful jump!
He demonstrates truly
remarkable talent
for a skater of any age.
[YAKOV] Even when he
doesn't skate his best,
he knows how to analyze
his performance mid-program
and make a comeback.
[LILIA] Beautiful.
You are a work of art.
Maintain that pride
until the very end.
[PLISETSKY]
Keep going.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[MOROOKA] His supporters here
in Moscow expected a lot,
and Yuri Plisetsky delivered it
with an exceptional
short program!
--[sputters]
--[PLISETSKY FANGIRLS squeal]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ladies first, please.
[PLISETSKY growls]
[PLISETSKY] I forgot there
was someone more annoying
than those other idiots--JJ.
Yeah, I'm feeling pretty--
[MOROOKA]
Yuri Plisetsky's score is 98.09,
putting him in second place.
Yuri Katsuki remains in first.
Today's final skater is the one
with the most momentum going
into this competition.
Jean-Jacques Leroy
of Canada, age 19.
Also known as "JJ."
[MOROOKA] He will be skating
to an original song
composed for him:
"Theme of King JJ."
["Theme of King JJ" plays]
[JEAN-JACQUES] Not just anyone
can pull off a collaboration
with a world-famous rock band.
This is the kind of program
that only King JJ can deliver.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Quadruple toe loop.
Triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA] Some major jumps
right off the bat.
JJ placed third at last
year's Grand Prix Final
and took first this
year at Skate Canada,
putting him in a solid position.
[JEAN-JACQUES] Hmph! Hope you're
ready for another big one.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
Incredible height!
He nearly cleared the
fence with that jump.
[JEAN-JACQUES chuckles] A lot of
top skaters load the second half
of their programs with jumps,
but I'm different.
I don't rely on that trick.
To me it's more important
that my skating
and the music work together.
It's JJ Style!
["Theme of King JJ" continues]
[JEAN-JACQUES laughs]
Let's go! Everyone, sing along!
[JEAN-JACQUES FANGIRLS]
♪ ...the world, JJ ♪
♪ Just follow me ♪
♪ I will break the walls ♪
♪ Now look at me. ♪
[MOROOKA]
The lyrics suggest that
JJ is at the top of the world,
and they invite everyone
to join him there.
An impressive step sequence.
[MOROOKA] Now, his last jump
is one that not even
Victor Nikiforov attempted in
the second half of his program.
It's a quadruple Lutz.
[MOROOKA]
He did it!
[JEAN-JACQUES] Nobody else takes
the kind of risks that I do.
I'm the only one
who can handle it.
Why? Because I'm the king!
I never stand still.
I never settle.
I wouldn't know how to,
even if I tried!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[JEAN-JACQUES FANGIRLS cheering]
Huh?
That's right--JJ Style!
[MARI] Hey, Yuri, I'm sorry
to call during an event,
but Makka got into
the steamed buns,
and one of 'em got
stuck in his throat.
Anyway, we're at
the vet right now,
but they're not sure
he's going to make it.
[MOROOKA] Jean-Jacques Leroy's
score is 113.56.
That surpasses his personal
best from Skate Canada!
[MARI] I'm sorry.
What do you want us to do?
[YURI] Victor! You need
to get back to Japan.
I can handle the free skate
tomorrow on my own.
Don't eat too many pirozhkis
tomorrow, all right?
Da, da.
[YURI]
You know you have to go back!
I already told you, I can't.
[PLISETSKY]
What's with them?
[VICTOR sighs]
[VICTOR]
Yakov!
That's it, thank God!
I'm so glad you're here!
You are the coach for me!
What's this?
Crawling back already?
It will just be for tomorrow.
For one day only,
will you be Yuri's coach?
Huh?
[YURI, YAKOV, PLISETSKY]
Huh?!
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY]
Eat some pirozhkis, Yurochka.
There are plenty.
[YURI]
Can I have one?
[PLISETSKY]
Stay away from my pirozhkis.
[YURI]
You haven't changed, have you?
[PLISETSKY]
Next time, Ninth Skate
[YURI] "Yuri vs...
[PLISETSKY] ...Yuri.
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY]
The Horror!!
[YURI, PLISETSKY]
Rostelecom Cup, Free Skate."