[YURI] Over the years, he has
never ceased to surprise me.
From the first time
I saw him skate,
till now, it's been one
surprise after another.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[MOROOKA]
Sure enough,
he's crushed the
free skating event, as well.
This marks the fifth consecutive
Grand Prix Final win
for Russian legend
Victor Nikiforov.
[MOROOKA]
Nikiforov is now 27 years old.
Some speculate that he
might retire this season,
but his masterful
performance here
may lay such rumors to rest.
Now let's talk
about Yuri Katsuki,
who was here competing in his
very first Grand Prix Final.
What are your thoughts, Honda?
[HONDA]
I hate to say it,
but he didn't perform
like his usual self today.
[CELESTINO]
Put that down!
Looking at the news
won't do you any good.
"Katsuki tumbles to last place.
Will this season be his
last one? Possibly."
[CELESTINO]
Yuri.
Huh?
[photo snap]
[YURI]
My name is Yuri Katsuki.
At 23, I'm one of the
dime-a-dozen figure skaters
certified by the JSF.
I had high hopes,
but I came in last at
my first Grand Prix Final.
I'm still having a
hard time accepting that.
I moved to Detroit to
train at a top-notch facility
and worked hard to qualify.
But before the match,
the pressure got to me,
and I started binge-eating.
Then the family dog died.
I was a complete wreck.
So my big day
became a big failure.
Man. Talk about self-sabotage.
Huh? Hello?
Hey, Mom.
Were you sleeping? Sorry.
Yeah. I figured
you'd seen it on TV.
What? You had a viewing party?
You've gotta be kidding,
Mom! I'm gonna die!
[YURI chuckles nervously]
Uh... Umm...
[sniffles]
I'm sorry... I messed up.
[sniffs]
[grunts]
[cries]
[YURI gasps]
[YURI sniffs]
Sorry.
[YURI] The Junior Grand
Prix Final Gold Medalist--
Yuri Plisetsky.
They call him
the "Russian Punk."
Why does he look like he's
trying to decide whether
or not to punch me?
[PLISETSKY]
Hey.
I'll be competing in the
senior division next year.
Maybe it's time
for you to retire.
I don't think we need two
Yuris in the same bracket.
Loser!
Tch!
[YURI]
Who would care if I did retire?
There are dozens of
talented young skaters
who could take my place.
[MOROOKA]
Hey, Katsuki!
[YURI]
Hi, Morooka.
Don't give up yet, kid,
you hear me?
You're too young to retire.
It's a little early for that.
I haven't even
made a decision yet.
[MOROOKA] What are your plans
after you graduate from college?
Uh...
[MOROOKA]
Are you staying in Detriot?
[YURI] I have to talk that
over with Coach Celestino.
[MOROOKA]
Listen to me!
You've got some
real thinking to do.
[YURI]
I don't want to think.
I'm sorry, Victor.
I wish I could've said goodbye.
[VICTOR]
Yuri.
[YURI gasps]
You did well tonight,
but I think your step sequence
could use a bit more finesse.
[PLISETSKY] I won, didn't I?
So who really cares?
Quit nagging me already.
[YURI]
Of course.
He meant the Russian Yuri.
Maybe I'll get the chance
to talk to him--someday.
[VICTOR]
Hmm?
[gasps]
You want to get a photo?
U-Uh...
Sure thing.
Huh?
[MOROOKA]
Where are you going?
Don't you want
a photo with Victor?
[CELESTINO]
Yuri!
[YURI]
I'm an idiot.
Did I seriously think I could
play on the same field as him?
Of course I ended up
getting humiliated.
[YURI]
"Easy as Pirozhki!
The Grand Prix Final of Tears."
[YURI]
It's been five years
since my last visit to Hasetsu.
This old station even
has elevated tracks now.
[gasps]
[YURI]
Oh, god!
Yuri! Why are you
skulking around like that?
Hey! What are you doing here?
Welcome home,
after five long years!
That's really not necessary.
Stand straight
and smile, woudja?
[YURI]
Why am I surprised?
I should've figured Minako would
know my exact arrival time.
[MALE STUDENT A]
Hey!
Huh?!
Isn't that Yuri, the ice skater?
It sure looks like him to me.
[MAN A] I haven't heard
much about him lately.
What's he been up to?
[WOMAN A] He lost that big
competition last year, remember?
[MAN B]
Was it the Nationals?
[photo snap]
[YURI] Hi, everyone
who cheered me on
just because I'm from Hasetsu!
I can't bring myself
to say this out loud,
but here's how the
last year's gone for me.
The figure skating competition
season generally starts
in the fall, but I lost big
in the comprehensive
Grand Prix Finals early on.
I couldn't shake off the failure
and lost again in the Nationals.
I didn't make it into
the Four Continents
or the World Championships,
so the season's over for me!
I managed to graduate college,
but I ended things with my
coach, and my future's unclear.
I came home 'til
I could figure things out,
and there ya have it.
[MAN C] Let me shake
your hand, young man.
Uh, sorry, I would,
but I'm in a hurry.
Hey! It doesn't cost you
anything to shake hands,
does it?
Victor Nikiforov's nice to
his fans, and you will be too.
Ya understand me?
Uh... I appreciate your support.
Now come on, let's see a smile.
Sorry, who are you again, dear?
[MINAKO] All right! You're
going to greet everyone in town!
[YURI]
Isn't there a ballet class
you need to be
teaching or something?
Nope we're closed today.
Anyway...
It's not like I have
very many students left.
Hasetsu's losing
more and more people.
Hardly any kids
are skating these days.
Having you back should
cheer things up, though!
Uh!
I'm sorry.
I'd really just like to rest.
What? Now?
But everyone's dying to see you.
[MOROOKA]
After the men's short program
of the World Figure
Skating Championships,
Russia's Victor Nikiforov
is in first place.
[PRESS shriek]
[MOROOKA]
After the Grand Prix Finals,
he went on to win the Russian
and European Championships.
As we've seen here,
he's still on a roll.
Men's free program starts
tonight at seven.
[MALE CUSTOMER A] They didn't
say anything about Yuri.
Isn't he competing?
No, he didn't qualify.
But fortunately for us, that
means he can come home.
[MALE CUSTOMER A]
Well, I'm happy for ya.
[YURI]
I'm home.
Hiroko! You'll never
guess who I have with me!
There you are, Minako!
Thank you for going
to get him at the station!
Yuri! Welcome home!
Yeah, thanks, Mom.
It's been a long time.
I should've come
to visit sooner, sorry.
None of that, now!
I only wish I could have
made it to your graduation!
Want a pork cutlet bowl?
You know, you look
like you've lost weight.
[HIROKO]
You're so sweet to an old lady!
What about you?
No matter how much you drink,
you don't seem to gain a pound!
As for you. What kind of gut
are you hiding underneath
that bulky coat of yours?
[YURI]
Ah!
All right, off with the clothes!
[shrieks]
No! Don't! Please stop!
Aaaah!
[YURI chuckles nervously]
Wow, you look just
like your mom, Yuri!
[YURI]
Dad.
This is no laughing
matter, Toshiya.
A figure skater has to
maintain a certain physique,
and that isn't it!
You've gained weight easily
ever since you were a boy.
But what can you do?
Now, how many pork cutlet bowls
should we put you down for?
Well, before I eat...
Of course, dear.
We understand.
Go pay your respects.
[YURI]
I'm sorry, boy.
I wish I could have
seen you one last time.
[door sliding open]
So you decided to
come home after all.
[YURI]
Mari. Hi.
[MARI]
Hmph.
You guys seem busy. I hope
I'm not getting in the way.
Nah, don't worry.
How long you staying, anyway?
You gonna help out
with the hot spring?
Well, I don't know.
You got your degree, even
though it took an extra year.
So what're you gonna do with it?
I mean, if you want to keep
skating I'll support you, but--
I guess. I kinda need
more time to think it over.
Sure. Okay.
Well, go soak in the hot spring.
You kinda look
like you could use it.
[YURI] I was born and raised
here in Hasetsu, Kyushu.
A castle town by the sea.
The "castle" isn't so much
a castle as a façade
with a ninja house inside.
The town used to have a
number of hot spring inns,
but most have gone under.
My family's Yu-topia
Akatsuki is the last one.
Ahh... This is exactly
what I needed.
[MOROOKA] Group Two has
now finished skating...
[MINAKO] Man, I really wanted
to go to the championships.
If only you'd qualified, Yuri,
you could've gotten me
the skaters' room numbers.
[YURI]
So that's it.
You support me in hopes
that I'll make it easier
for you to stalk hot skaters.
[MINAKO] Hey! That's only one
of the reasons I support you!
[MOROOKA]
He will be skating last.
Well, Honda, what do you think
we can expect from him tonight?
[HONDA] If anyone
can clench this fifth title...
There's a soccer match.
Sagan Tosu. Let's switch.
You can change the channel
when I'm done watching skating.
Sagan Tosu?
Better keep working
or you'll get in trouble.
Hey, you just got here,
and you're leaving already?
[YURI] Sorry. I wanted
to get some practice in.
[HIROKO]
All right, dear, take care.
[YURI]
Excuse me.
[YUKO]
Sorry, we're closed.
You can come back tomorrow.
[YURI] Hey, Yuko.
Long time no see, huh?
[YUKO]
That you, Yuri?
Well, quit standing
there like some stranger
and tell me how you've been!
Fine, I guess.
Well, I bet you
came to skate, huh?
Go right ahead.
[YURI]
Really? You don't mind?
[YUKO] Nah. I'm guessing
you don't want an audience?
I'll make sure
you're not interrupted.
Great, thanks a lot.
[YUKO]
Hmm!
[YURI]
Yuko's two years older than me.
She was my rink mate.
She was a really great
skater when we were little.
I grew up idolizing her.
The Madonna of
Ice Castle Hasetsu.
She's still as pretty as ever.
Yay!
Wow! Great job!
[laughs]
[NISHIGORI grunts]
Move it you're in my way, fatso!
Stop!
Picking on the new kid doesn't
make you look tough, you know!
Fatso! Fatso!
Hey!
[YUKO]
Russia's Victor Nikiforov!
He won the gold
in the Junior Worlds
with the highest
score in history!
He's amazing!
Aaahh...!
[YUKO]
This is how Victor would do it!
According to this,
Victor has a poodle.
You see? Right there.
--[YUKO] Isn't he adorable?
--[YURI] What a cute dog!
[barks]
Aw! Is this sweet
little ball of fluff yours?
Yeah, and I named him Victor.
[laughs] You really are Victor's
number one fan, aren't you?
I hope that you get to compete
against him someday.
I'd really like to see it.
[YURI]
Um...
There's something
I really want you to see.
I've been practicing this ever
since the competitions ended.
Will you watch?
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[MOROOKA] Last up:
Victor Nikiforov from Russia.
[RANDOM WOMAN A]
Victor!
[MINAKO] All right, Victor!
Give 'em hell!
Where's Yuri, anyway?
His darling Victor's up!
I don't think he's back yet.
Wait. That opening.
["Stay Close to Me" plays]
[MOROOKA]
He has an ambitious program,
with four quads planned.
Here comes his first.
Let's see if he lands it.
[MOROOKA] A quadruple Lutz!
Nice, very clean!
The next quad is his signature
move, a real crowd favorite.
Here we go!
A quadruple flip,
and he nails it!
[MOROOKA]
Flying sit spin.
[MOROOKA] The song he's
chosen is "Stay Close to Me."
I wonder how many women are
watching this now and drooling.
About a million? I mean,
he is one fine specimen.
[HIROKO] I think you've had
enough to drink, Minako.
[MOROOKA]
Flawless Quad Sal!
[MINAKO] I don't know
if this is the best music
for a worldly man
like him, though.
It would work better for
a dewy-eyed youngster.
Ya know?
[MOROOKA]
A triple Lutz.
A triple flip!
[gasps]
[MOROOKA]
Now, the last quad is coming up.
A quadruple toe loop,
followed by a triple toe loop!
That's it! He did it.
He landed all his quads!
[MOROOKA] Now all that's
left is a combination spin.
[pants]
Oh...!
Huh...?!
[YUKO]
You're freaking amazing!
That was a
perfect copy of Victor!
[chuckles] Honestly,
I thought you'd be depressed.
[YURI]
I was,
but it turns out being depressed
gets pretty old after a while.
I lost my love for skating,
and I wanted it back.
I thought if I copied Victor
like we did in the old days,
it would help.
Yuko. I've been thinking...
[MOROOKA]
With his fifth consecutive gold
in the World Figure
Skating Championships,
Victor Nikiforov has made
history here tonight!
[FEMALE INTERVIEWER A] What
do you think the next season
will hold for you?
[VICTOR]
Hmm...
[YURI]
The thing is--
[TRIPLETS]
Stare.
My girls, Axel, Lutz, and Loop.
They're a lot bigger than the
last time you saw them,
aren't they?
[YURI]
Uh, Yeah...
Wow, you really
did get fat, Yuri!
So you're retiring?
You've never had a girlfriend?
Hey! Ignore them!
The girls are groupies, sorry!
Ha! I'm telling ya, those three
are some of your biggest fans.
Hey!
Nishigori!
[TRIPLETS]
Daddy!
You're fatter than me!
Stop, This isn't funny!
[NISHIGORI]
Come by to practice any time.
The Nishigori family's always
got your back, you know that
[LOOP]
You can do it, Yuri!
[AXEL]
Work hard!
[LUTZ]
Lose weight!
[YURI]
A lot happened while I was away.
For the most part, I ignored it.
I focused on skating
and nothing else.
[grunts]
[YURI]
I wish I knew what to do now.
I want to keep skating.
But can I do it on my own?
[MOROOKA]
Here in St. Petersburg, Russia,
rising star Yuri
Plisetsky is gearing up
in earnest to join
the senior competition.
Whoa! Did you see that jump?
No, make that two jumps.
[MOROOKA] ...the 15-year-old
phenom may soon join the ranks
of Victor Nikiforov as one of
the world's preeminent
male figure skaters.
Maybe it's time
for you to retire.
Oh...
[YURI]
I'm going to do it.
I'm not sure how,
but I'm going to skate
on the same ice as
Victor again someday.
[phone dings]
[YURI]
Huh? Nishigori?
What?!!
[NISHIGORI]
Look, Yuri. I'm really sorry.
The girls uploaded it,
and it's gone viral.
You know you're not supposed to
use my account without asking!
But Mommy, it'll make
the skater otaku so happy!
[YUKO]
Just delete it, okay?
Goodnight.
You thought you could become
an internet sensation
without telling me?
Katsuki?! Are you kidding me
with this video, or what?
[PHICHIT laughs]
Yuri!
What a clown.
Why doesn't he retire already?
[WEATHER LADY A] A sudden
cold front blew into Kyushu,
turning what should have been
beautiful cherry blossom viewing
weather into a
snowy tundra overnight.
[HIROKO] You can't just
hole up in your room forever.
Come out and
help shovel the snow!
[YURI]
Snow?
Whoa! She wasn't kidding!
This late in the year?
No weather alert?
Right. I turned it off,
so I wouldn't get any calls.
[dog barking]
Huh? Victor?
Whoa! Aah!
Ahh...
You're too big!
You couldn't be Victor.
Huh?
Hold on...
This dog looks exactly like--No.
There's no way.
[TOSHIO]
Morning!
Looks just like our Victor, eh?
His owner's a new guest,
some good-looking young
fellow with an accent.
He's in the spring right now.
You okay?
Hey! Where are you going?
[STRANGER sighs]
Vi... Victor...
[VICTOR]
Hmm...
Why are you here?
Hello, Yuri. Starting today,
I'm going to be your new coach.
You're going to get
to the Grand Prix Final.
And you're going to win.
Huh? Whaaaat?!!
[YURI]
Not once over the years
has he ever ceased
to surprise me.
[PLISETSKY] Hey, Victor!
We're going back to Russia!
[VICTOR]
Hasetsu's great. I mean it!
You really should visit.
[TRIPLETS]
Rub Yuri's belly!
[VICTOR] Seriously,
nice weather...
[YURI]
No, no, no, no, no!
[YURI, PLISETSKY]
Next time, Second Skate.
"Two Yuris? Drama at Yu-topia."