[YAKOV]
Vitya! Don't do this!
Can't we talk?
[VICTOR] Yakov, you are
the best coach I ever had.
Nothing will change that.
[YAKOV] If you walk away now,
you can never come back!
Dasvidanya . I'm sorry, but
this time I can't do as you say.
What d'you mean this time?
You've never done what I said
once since I've known you!
If you happen to be in Japan,
drop by and see me!
[YURI]
"Two Yuris? Drama at Yu-topia!"
Where is he?
Why isn't he answering his cell?
You seem upset, dear,
is something wrong?
[MINAKO]
The world is going insane!
There's a rumor saying
that Victor is going
to be Yuri's coach.
Well, I guess that explains
what he's doing here, then.
Huh?
[HIROKO]
Just look at him!
He's sleeping soundly as a baby.
[photo snap]
[YURI]
Hey there! I'm Yuri Katsuki.
I'm in a bit of
a slump right now,
but I'm actually a
top JSF figure skater.
Back home for the
first time in five years,
I was trying to think of
a way to revive my career.
When out of nowhere my idol,
Victor, showed up!
Is this happening?
I must be dreaming, right?
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[YURI]
In case you don't already know,
Victor Nikiforov is a
legend in figure skating.
I never thought for a second
that he would have
any interest in me, but...
[VICTOR] Starting today, I'm
going to be your new coach.
You're going to get
to the Grand Prix Final.
And you're going to win.
[YURI]
He's naked. So very naked.
[MINAKO]
Yuri!
And why's he passed out on the
floor in one of the inn's robes?
After soaking in the hot
spring and eating dinner,
he just sort of fell asleep.
[MINAKO] It's all over
the news in Russia.
They say he's taking
the next season off
to consider the
future of his career.
But what's really
interesting is the reason.
Apparently, he saw the video
of you skating his routine.
He was so inspired
by your performance,
he decided to become your coach.
Huh?
[MINAKO]
That's why he's here.
He chose you to
become his protégé.
Do you know how
incredible that is?
He came for you!
Hmm...
[PLISETSKY]
What?
He seriously went
all the way to Japan
to become the
other Yuri's coach?
Yuri Katsuki?
The fat pig?
Did that jerk forget the
promise he made to me?
Geh!
Yakov!
Where are you?
I want an explanation!
[YAKOV]
Victor is taking some time off
to reassess his career goals.
I believe this
break is ill-advised
and that he will have
a hard time returning.
[MALE REPORTER A]
I hear he's gone to Japan
to coach Yuri Katsu--
Victor doesn't think
of anyone but himself.
He could never
be somebody's coach!
[sneezes]
[YURI, MINAKO gasp]
He's awake!
Is there more food
around here?
I'm so hungry.
I thought you said he ate.
Sure, we've got lots of food!
What would you like?
What's your favorite food, Yuri?
If I'm going to be your coach,
that's something I ought
to know, don't you think?
Oh...
[VICTOR]
Wow! This looks amazing!
This is our specialty,
the pork cutlet bowl!
[VICTOR]
Vkusno !
Really! There are no words!
This must be what God eats!
Glad you like it so much.
The rule was he could only eat
it after winning a competition
since he gains weight so easily.
Oh, really? Tell me, have you
had a pork cutlet bowl recently?
Sure! They're my favorite,
so I eat them all the time.
Oh, yeah? But you haven't
won anything, have you?
There's not a lot I can
do with you until you lose
that piggy gut and
work off those love handles.
You need to get
back to your weight
at last year's Grand
Prix Final, at the least.
Or I can't coach you.
So, why don't you lay off
the pork cutlet bowls?
Okay, little piggy?
Uh-huh! I feel like
I should be insulted.
Hey, Yuri. What's up
with all these boxes?
Think you can take them to
the room where I'll be staying?
Say what now?
Ah! What an incredibly
adorable little room!
Is there a sofa?
No, sorry.
I know it's really small,
but it's the only room
that we had available.
I'll make it work,
don't you worry.
Oh, and we can defer
my coaching fee for now.
I'll bill you once
you've won something.
Okay. Thank you.
[VICTOR]
Now, then.
I want to know
everything about you, Yuri.
Like what kind
of rink you skate at.
And what hobbies do you have.
And if there's a girl you like.
Let's get to know each other.
A relationship like this
should be built on trust,
don't you think?
[shrieks]
What's wrong?
Why'd you run away?
[YURI]
Uh. I had a leg cramp.
[YURI] I still can't
handle being close to him.
[VICTOR] Yuri, let's
have a slumber party!
Come on, open up!
It's the perfect way for us to
learn more about each other.
[YURI]
No!
[VICTOR]
Yuri! Yuri! Yuri?
[YURI]
We've barely ever spoken.
He seemed like a glittering god,
beyond my reach.
And now he's right here!
I just realized--the reason my
heart's pounding is I'm happy.
[pants]
Hello there!
Hey!
[VICTOR]
Hello!
I'll be Yuri's coach
from now on. Victor Nikiforov.
Nice to meet you!
Huh? Huh? Huh?!
Victor's really going
to coach you?!
[YUKO]
Wow! A quadruple flip! Amazing!
I got a great shot!
I've got awesome video.
How soon can
we upload this, Huh?
This isn't for
the public, fangirls!
So this is for real.
Mm-hmm. He says
he'd like to use this
as our primary training
rink for now. That okay?
I'll talk to the higher-ups, but
I'm sure it won't be a problem.
Victor teaching you himself must
be a dream come true, huh?
[YURI]
When I was 12, Victor was 16
and already the top male
singles skater in the world.
I've imitated him for years,
trying to equal his genius.
And now I find out that
watching a video of me
somehow inspired him ?
That doesn't even seem possible.
What was it?
What did you see in me?
Remember, you're not
setting foot in this rink
until you drop
some weight, little piggy.
[YURI]
Not exactly awesome
in the pep talk department,
though, is he?
[MINAKO]
Maybe he was just looking
for an excuse to take a break.
Come on, don't say that.
It's what I think too,
but I don't like hearing it.
[MINAKO] Listen. You want
to keep skating, don't you?
Uh.
Then you need all
the help you can get!
Now, let's trim off
some fat, shall we?
Yeah. Okay.
[YURI] These days,
Minako is a ballet instructor.
But when she was younger,
she used to travel all
over the world as a dancer.
When I was younger, I went
to her studio all the time.
I spent more time in
her ballet class than at home.
She's the one who suggested
I start skating
in the first place.
She's always
been really supportive.
But she does like to meddle.
So, do you have
feelings for Minako?
Huh? No, no way!
Do you have a lover now?
No.
What about ex-lovers?
I'd rather not talk about it.
Then let's talk about me!
Let's see, my first lover--
[YURI]
Stop!
[sighs]
[MAKKACHIN barks]
[VICTOR]
Hmm?
Hey, Yuri. What's that
building up there?
People call it Hasetsu Castle,
but inside it's really
a ninja house!
Huh?! Really? No way!
Hasetsu Castle!
I wanna see!
[MAN A] Now there's
an enthusiastic tourist.
[VICTOR]
Ninja! Yes!
[PLISETSKY]
Hasetsu Castle?
Does he wanna be
a ninja or something?
Okay. Now I know where he is.
Just wait, Victor.
I'll see you soon.
[hums]
Oh?
[MARI]
Huh?
So Is it true that
Victor's staying at this inn?
[RANDOM WOMAN A]
Can we take a bath with him?
I don't remember the last time
we had this many customers!
[RANDOM MALE REPORTER C]
Is Victor here? Please!
Can we talk to him?
[RANDOM MALE REPORTER D] We'd
like to film a special feature!
What the hell is
going on here?
[RANDOM WOMAN D] I can't
believe how beautiful he is!
[WOMAN A]
Excuse me, can I get a photo?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Victor's at Ice Castle!
Can you freakin' believe it?
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
So hot!
[PLISETSKY]
Wow. Creepy.
Oh, crap.
If I post this,
Yakov'll know I'm here and
come to haul me back.
[PLISETSKY] This is
the city that was tagged
in all the pics
Victor's been uploading.
Hey! Victor come out!
Do you hear me?
Whoa!
That shirt. I want it now!
[YAKOV]
Yuri!
Would you like to explain to me
what the hell you're
doing in Japan?
Whoops. You found out?
[YAKOV] You're not in the junior
leagues any more, idiot!
You should be training!
Don't tell me what to do!
I'm not coming back to Russia
until Victor makes good
on his promise to me!
Man. He's such a nag.
I can handle myself without
any help from that geezer.
[PLISETSKY]
I'm supposed to do
a triple Salchow, but...
Don't even think about it, Yuri.
[PLISETSKY]
I can do it.
[AUDIENCE claps]
A Quadruple Salchow?
[PLISETSKY]
See that, Yakov?
You idiot! How many
times to I have to tell you
quads are strictly
off-limits until you're older?
If you can't follow orders,
then maybe you should quit!
[laughs]
Go easy.
Don't be so tough
on him all the time.
This has nothing
to do with you, Victor!
I know how you feel. I got
yelled at for doing that, too.
But you can win,
even without doing quads.
I'd bet money on it.
I think you can win
the Junior Worlds'.
Okay, if I win without
doing any quads,
I want you to choreograph
a program, just for me!
[VICTOR]
It's a deal.
After you win the Junior World
Championship, come see me.
I'll make sure you have
the best senior debut ever.
Huh?! Where am I?
Hey, Victor!
Oh? Are you a fan of Victor's?
He spends a lot
of time practicing
at the skating rink
below the castle.
I would try there.
[RANDOM WOMAN F]
Come on, just let us watch!
[AXEL] The rink is reserved
for a private practice session.
[LUTZ]
Yeah, go home already!
Hey, you, bub!
No one's allowed in there!
[PLISETSKY]
What?
Yuri Plisetsky!
[RANDOM WOMAN G]
The junior world champion!
[TRIPLETS]
Huh?
If Victor's in there, I wanna
see him.
[TRIPLETS]
Of course, O Great One!
[YURI pants]
I made it. And I didn't die.
Yuri.
Hey, girls, guess what.
My weight's back to what it was
before the Grand Prix Final.
Now Victor will finally
give me permission to skate!
Augh!
Huh...? My face!
All of this is
your stupid fault!
Now say you're sorry!
[YURI]
What's he doing here?
And why's he standing
on my head?
[LOOP] The Japanese Yuri and the
Russian Yuri in the same place.
[AXEL]
This is perfect!
[LUTZ] Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
Heee...
[PLISETSKY]
A long time ago Victor promised
he'd choreograph
a program for me.
He promise you, too?
Uh, we haven't
exactly gotten around
to talking about programs.
Huh? If you're not
working on a new program,
then what have you been doing?
Why's he wasting time on you?
If he knew about
your little sob-fest
in the bathroom
at the Grand Prix,
he'd realize there's no point in
training a big crybaby like you.
[YURI]
The Russian Punk.
Maybe it's time
for you to retire.
Hmph!
[YURI]
He's really underestimating me.
I don't know what history
you and Victor have.
You should talk to him yourself.
It's not like I made
Victor come to Hasetsu.
He came because
he wanted to be my coach.
[gasps]
[PLISETSKY]
I recognize those moves.
They're for the
short program Victor
was choreographing
for next season.
What?
Before he decided to come here,
he was putting together
routines for next season.
But he was really torn.
Surprising the audience
has always been
what he cared most about.
For years the skating
world has worshipped him.
Now, no matter what he does,
no one's surprised anymore.
He knows that and
it really eats at him.
He doesn't feel inspired,
and without inspiration
you're as good as dead.
I wonder if he'll
let me use his program.
He doesn't need it if he's
gonna take off this season.
Huh?
If he'll give me a chance,
I know I can
surprise the audience.
I'm going to make
my debut as a senior
and win the Grand Prix Final.
But I need
Victor's help to do it!
[gasps]
Wow. You're confident.
Hey Victor, you got
time for a little chat?
Hey, I didn't know
you were here!
I'm surprised
Yakov let you come.
You need something?
Uh-oh! That's not a happy face!
Let me guess: I forgot to do
something I said I would do?
[laughs]
Yeah, I remember now.
It totally slipped my mind!
I'm sorry, but you know
how I forget stuff sometimes.
[PLISETSKY]
Yeah. I'm painfully aware.
But I'm holding you
to your promise.
You'll choreograph my
new program like you said.
We're going back to Russia!
[YURI]
Eh... Huh?!
[VICTOR]
Hmm...
Okay, I've got it!
I'm going to choreograph
a program for both of you--
to the same music.
Huh?!
--The same music as this guy?
--Choreograph both of us?
Now, don't worry boys,
this piece has two
different arrangements.
I've just been trying
to decide which one to use.
I'll design two programs
using different portions
of the same song.
The programs will
be revealed in one week.
The two of you will
compete to see which one
can surprise
the audience more!
Whoa! A competition?
Is that really necessary?
The catch is, Victor has to
do whatever the winner wants.
What do you say?
Perfect! I love
this sort of thing!
[TRIPLETS]
Wait just a minute!
If you wanna use our rink,
you'd better let us in
on the action, you got me?
An epic face-off
between Russia and Japan.
It's gonna be big!
Let's get ready to rumble!
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER A]
We've got exciting news, folks!
In one week the special
exhibition "Hot Springs on Ice"
will premiere at
Ice Castle Hasetsu.
You don't want to miss a once-
in-a-lifetime event like this!
This place is a real hovel.
So, where's my room, anyway?
Wait a sec! You're staying here?
No way I'm letting you
have Victor to yourself
all the time, fatso.
So I'm staying here, okay?
If I say no, is there any
chance you'll actually leave?
The hot spring here
is just divine.
I'm not taking a bath with
other people. Now goodnight!
[stomach grumbling]
I want food and a bath.
[sighs]
So good!
Can't beat the pork cutlet bowl.
Jeez, Yuri, you
have another visitor?
Huh? Huh?!
Aaah!
[MARI] No way! He looks
like my idol, The Blond Takao!
His name is Yuri,
too, isn't that funny?
Huh? That's just
gonna be confusing.
We'll call you Yurio.
Huh?
So, where will
Yurio be sleeping?
[YURI]
Upstairs?
What, in the storage room?
It's gonna need a
major cleaning first.
Yuri, come help me.
[YURI]
Uh?
[VICTOR] Looks like
you have a fan, Yurio.
I'm not gonna
go by that stupid name!
[laughs]
[YURI]
Oh, man. I'm an idiot.
The other Yuri is the
one with all the potential.
He's so confident.
His first year
at the senior level,
and he's sure he'll
win the Grand Prix.
And he doesn't turn
into a blubbering mess
whenever Victor talks to him.
He belongs with Victor. Not me.
[VICTOR]
Hey, where's Yuri?
He headed out a while ago.
He either ran off
to Minako's place
or else down to Ice Castle.
It's what he does.
[MINAKO]
Huh? Yuri?
He's not here.
If she said my place,
she meant my ballet studio.
See, when Yuri gets anxious,
practicing chills him out.
So he goes down to the rink,
and I usually go with him.
Ice Castle lets
him skate anytime
if it's not already booked.
Yuri's always been
an anxious guy.
He only came as far as he did
because he had a safe place
where he could
practice on his own.
He's no genius,
but he works hard,
and he truly loves to skate.
[NISHIGORI] He's been
coming here to practice
by himself forever.
It shows you how much
he loves the sport, you know?
As a kid, he didn't even
play with his friends.
To be fair, it's not like
he was ever any good
at making friends to play with.
He's not great at
putting himself out there,
on or off the ice.
I don't want this
to be the end for him.
No, neither do I, the thing
you should know about Yuri is,
he's actually a
pretty sore loser.
I hope you can
bring out a side of him
that we've never seen before.
[VICTOR]
Hmm...
So all I have
to do is find a way
to turn a piggy into a prince?
[NISHIGORI, YUKO]
Huh?
[VICTOR]
Nothing. Never mind.
Thanks. I feel like
I know Yuri a lot better know.
[VICTOR]
Lovely day, isn't it?
Morning, Victor.
[VICTOR]
Be polite, Yurio. Say hi!
I told you I'm not
answering to that name!
[YURI]
Victor's finally going to
start coaching me today!
This'll decide whether
or not it's my last season.
If I wuss out now, I'm done.
[YURI] First, I'm going to be
the Hot Springs on Ice champion.
And then, I'll set my sights
on the Grand Prix Final!
We will start by
listening to the music.
[slow song playing]
[VICTOR] This piece
has two arrangements--
each with a different theme.
The title of it is
"On Love: Eros and Agape."
Have you ever spent much
time thinking about love?
Nyet .
[VICTOR]
All right, then.
How does this
song make you feel?
What does it say to you?
It has a very pure,
innocent sound to it,
like someone who hasn't
experienced love yet.
Whatever, I think it sucks.
This "innocence" crap
makes me wanna puke. Blurgh!
[VICTOR]
Okay.
[upbeat song plays]
Wow, this sounds like
a completely different song.
[PLISETSKY]
I call dibs!
This is the one
I want to skate to.
[VICTOR] The first arrangement
is "On Love: Agape."
The theme is unconditional love.
[YURI gulps]
This is "On Love: Eros."
And the theme of
it is sexual love.
[PLISETSKY]
Hmph!
[VICTOR] I am going to
have the two of you skate
to these opposing themes.
Here are your assignments.
You get Eros.
You get Agape.
We should switch!
That's so not me!
You should always try
to do the exact opposite
of what people are
expecting from you.
How else can you surprise them?
That's my motto.
The truth is:
you're actually both far more
mediocre than you think.
You need to be more self-aware.
I'm surprised you don't
realize how much work
you both need
to do on your images.
Right now to the audience you're
just a piglet and a kitten.
You had better be up to
my standards by next week.
Or I won't continue
to work with either of you.
But don't worry, as fans of
mine, I'm sure you'll manage.
[PLISETSKY]
Okay, fine.
I'll skate to "Agape." My senior
division debut depends on it.
But you had better give me
a program that I can win with!
Whether you win
or not is up to you.
It would be a winning
program if I skated it.
If I win, you are coming
back to Russia with me. Okay?
And you'll be my coach. Well,
do you accept those terms?
Hmm. I do.
[gasps]
Hmph!
Well, what do you want from me?
If you win, what is your reward?
To eat with you--pork
cutlet bowls.
Huh?
I want to keep on winning
and keep on eating
pork cutlet bowls!
So I'll skate to "Eros," Victor!
And I'll give it all
the eros I've got in me!
[VICTOR] Good!
That's what I like to hear!
[VICTOR] I wonder which of you
will be able to satisfy me.
[YURI]
I will! I'm sure of it!
[PLISETSKY]
I'll believe it when I see it!
Don't underestimate Russia!
[YURI, PLISETSKY]
Next time, Third Skate.
"I am Eros, and Eros is Me?
Face-Off! Hot Springs on Ice!"