[YURI]
Hey there!
Yuri Katsuki here.
I'm getting ready for my first
competition of the season,
the Chu-Shikoku-Kyushu
Regional Championship.
There are four of us in
the senior men's division,
and I'm the oldest...
by a lot.
Anything but first!
[EVENT STAFF A] Skater
Yuri Katsuki, you're up first.
[YURI]
No, not again.
Just like the last Nationals.
I have the worst luck
with this sort of thing.
I can't believe
I got to watch you
draw your spot two
years in a row!
Lucky me!
And you're?
[KENJIRO] Wait a sec, you
mean you don't remember me?
My heart just broke a little!
Kenjiro Minami, right here!
[YURI]
Who's he again?
Woo-hoo!
Looks like I'm skating last!
[YURI]
"Face Beet-Red!!
It's the First Competition!
The Chu-Shikoku-Kyushu
Regional Championship."
No pressure.
We've timed the season, so he
peaks at the Grand Prix Final.
So today he can take it easy.
His focus will be on
scoring his personal best.
I must've told
you a million times,
but in last year's Nationals,
I bombed everything.
I did so incredibly bad,
they thought I was injured,
but there was nothing
physically wrong.
Do you understand?
Despite being a top contender,
I lost because
I was mentally weak.
But no pressure, right?
[VICTOR]
Wow.
[YURI] I haven't been
in a single competition
since last year's Nationals.
Look, even Makka's
here to cheer for you!
[YURI]
I've been training with Victor
for a while now.
[VICTOR]
Such a grumpy pants!
[YURI]
But honestly,
I'm still not all
that sure of myself.
This is the first test
I'll have to figure out
if I'm in good enough shape
for the Grand Prix series.
I need to concentrate on myself,
not the other skaters.
Ahhh...
[YURI] I can feel
somebody staring at me.
[KANAKO] Remember
how focused you were
at the Nationals last season?
Now's not the time
to get distracted!
[YURI]
Focus! Focus!
[MINAKO]
Wow.
Quite a turn-out, huh?
Been like this since
the public practice earlier.
[MINAKO]
I hope Yuri's okay.
He's usually a mess
before competitions. Oh!
You have any idea
where Victor is?
It's about to start,
and I can't find him.
Sorry, were you waiting?
[YURI] What did you
change your clothes for?
Today is my debut as a coach,
so I thought I should
dress for the occasion.
What, don't you like it?
[YURI]
Oh God.
That man preens like a peacock.
He stands out
more than the skaters
As your coach,
it's my duty send you out
there feeling confident.
I know it's been tough--but I
truly believe that you... Uh.
[YURI]
My goal is the Grand Prix Final.
I can't get nervous now.
I'm not nervous.
[MINAKO]
Hm? Oh, he's nervous.
[ANNOUNCER] Gentlemen,
the warm-up has ended.
Please make your way off the ice
so the competition can begin.
[YURI]
Hmm?
Why does he look so upset?
[VICTOR]
Yuri, I want you to turn around.
[YURI]
Huh?
I said, turn around.
Okay, like this?
[VICTOR] Seduce me with
everything you have.
If your performance
can enthrall me,
then you can bring the
whole audience to their knees.
That's what I say
in practice, right?
[YURI]
Right.
Go, Yuri!
Good luck!
[YURI] Remember: Skate like
you do in practice.
["On Love: Eros" plays]
[YURI]
You are the femme fatale
of the pork cutlet bowl.
You can do this.
[YURI]
Come on, people,
this is a pretty
lukewarm response.
The audience
was way more into it
during the Hot Springs
on Ice face-off.
Focus.
Victor always likes
this step sequence.
[VICTOR]
All right!
Imagine the juiciness of the
pork, the softness of the egg.
[YURI]
Got it!
Now, dance more like
you're trying to seduce me.
[YURI]
That's right.
I am a mouth-watering
pork cutlet bowl
that no man can refuse.
First up is a spread
eagle into a triple axel.
Nailed it.
Now onto the
quadruple Salchow.
[YURI]
Over-rotation!
I was drawn to you
because of the way
you move to the music.
Like the song's
already inside you
and you're using your
body to release it.
That's perfect.
[YURI]
The last jump is a combination
and worth the most points.
A quad into a triple.
Crap, made it a double.
This is the last element.
The conclusion to
the lovers' story.
Wait, how does it go, again?
Right, the temptress casts
aside the man she seduced
and moves on to
her next conquest.
[AUDIENCE claps]
That was awesome, Yuri!
You're amazing!
[YURI]
Who's that?
I managed to finish.
I wonder if I did okay.
What does Victor think?
The first half was great,
but then you became so
focused on landing the jumps
that your
performance got sloppy.
I don't really like
that sort of thing.
[YURI]
Right.
Why's he getting yelled at?
He had the audience
panting for him.
[NISHIGORI] Hm. He could be
looking at a personal best.
[ANNOUNCER] And now,
the scores for Yuri Katsuki.
Short program score: 94.36.
He is currently in first place.
That's almost ten points higher
than his previous best! Amazing!
Well, this won't
be an official record,
but that score is among
the top ten in the world!
[VICTOR]
Hm.
I thought you might be able
to get into the hundreds
since you weren't
under pressure.
Right, I mean you've broken
the world record multiple times
with scores in the hundreds,
so it must be easy.
[VICTOR] Oh, by the way,
about the free skate tomorrow.
Let's lower the jump difficulty
and focus on performance.
[YURI]
Huh?
[VICTOR]
Now, now, you know
you've never landed
them all in practice.
Victor.
Early on in the season,
it makes sense to lower
your program's difficulty.
Then you can adjust
as you go along
and time it to reach your
peak at the Grand Prix Final.
You wouldn't disobey
your coach, would you?
[MAKKACHIN barks]
[KENJIRO]
Incredible!
Yuri was obviously a
temptress who uses her wiles
to seduce and then to betray in
the most beautiful way possible!
You saw it, right, Kanako?
That triple axel!
That was a GOE of
3,000,000 points, easy!
[KANAKO]
Yeah.
I hope your triple axel
goes that well.
It's been inconsistent.
I want Yuri to be
impressed with my program,
so I have to nail it.
How do you feel looking
ahead to the free skate?
Uh, I'm hoping I'll be able to--
Yuri's focus will be on
flawless execution tomorrow.
Did you see that?
I managed to land
the triple axel.
I'd say that was easily
your best performance yet!
Hey! Did you see it?
My "Lohengrin" performance?
I was being interviewed,
so I missed it. Sorry.
[gasps, whimpers]
I even had a
special costume made.
It's similar to the one
from your famous
"Lohengrin" program?
A costume from my shameful past.
[KENJIRO gasps]
An amazing skater like you
doesn't have a shameful past!
When you make fun of yourself,
you're also making fun of me
for looking up to
you all this time.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna give
it everything I've got!
If you're the skater
I think you are, so will you!
If you slack off,
I won't forgive you!
Whoa!
It looks like Minami's throwing
down the gauntlet, folks!
Let's not forget,
at last year's Nationals,
he finished ahead
of skater Katsuki.
[YURI]
Oh, right. I remember now.
He's the guy who won last
year after I self-destructed.
Aw, crap.
The free skate program will
begin soon here in Okayama.
Everyone is eager to see
who today's champion will be.
All eyes are on Yuri Katsuki
and his coach Victor Nikiforov.
Hi!
[MOROOKA] Katsuki ended
yesterday's short program
in the lead by a wide margin,
scoring a personal best of
ninety-four point three six.
In his free skate today,
he will attempt three quads.
[YURI] Victor and I decided
to lower the difficulty
and only do one quad, but--
[KENJIRO]
Yuri's doing a quad.
I'm gonna try one too!
Seriously? But you've never
even landed one in practice.
[HIKARU]
Maybe I'll try it.
[YUTO]
Yeah, me too!
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the senior men's
free skate program.
Will the competitors please
take the ice for your warm-up?
You have six minutes.
Thank you.
[VICTOR]
Hm...
[YURI]
I can't get distracted.
I need to focus
on myself right now.
Yuri.
[YURI]
Huh?
If you don't have the strength
to motivate someone
who looks up to you,
how can you find the strength
to motivate yourself?
I'm disappointed in you.
[YURI] Can we talk about
what you just did
to my motivation for a second?
[ANNOUNCER]
Representing Hakata Skate Club.
Please welcome Kenjiro Minami.
[KANAKO]
Okay, you can do this.
Hey, are you listening to me?
Oh, you're nervous.
Good luck out there, Minami!
An amazing skater like you
doesn't have a shameful past!
When you make fun of yourself,
you're also making fun of me
for looking up
to you all this time.
[YURI sighs]
Hey, Minami!
Good luck!
[VICTOR]
Hm.
[energetic music plays]
[YURI]
The crowd's into it already.
He must be popular.
[KENJIRO]
First, a triple axel.
[YURI]
All right, one jump down.
[KENJIRO]
And now, a quadruple toe loop.
[YURI] Wow. Is he going
to land all of them?
[YURI]
He's good.
But still really inconsistent.
It reminds me of
the skater I used to be.
It's hard to take your
eyes off him, though.
[YURI]
He's got the skill set
to be a real competitor.
There's no doubting that.
[FANGIRLS cheering]
[YURI]
I can tell by their cheers--
[YURI] That you are
the star on the stage.
[AUDIENCE claps]
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER] Now the
scores for Kenjiro Minami.
His free skate program
score is 152.14.
That makes his total score...
Yeah! A new personal best score!
[ANNOUNCER]
Representing Kure Higashi
High School Skate Club,
please welcome Hikaru Fujiwara.
Good luck!
[HIKARU, GRAY JACKET MAN]
All right!
[ANNOUNCER]
Representing Okayama...
'Kay. Let's do this.
Yeah!
Skate well!
[inhales]
[exhales]
Way to go.
Keep it up, and it'll
be a personal best.
Oh!
[shrieks]
Good. I think this
costume was the right choice.
You look absolutely stunning.
Your lips are a little chapped.
[laughs]
I heard Victor wanted
him to cut it down
to one quad this time,
but I wonder if that's
going to happen.
Yeah, Yuri's a stubborn ass
when he wants to be.
Go, Yuri! Good luck!
In this first public performance
of Katsuki's free program,
he will be skating
to an original composition
inspired by his skating career.
It is titled "Yuri on Ice."
The program was choreographed
by Victor Nikiforov.
["Yuri on Ice" plays]
[VICTOR] The opening of the
program expresses the time
in Yuri's career when he felt
like he was fighting alone.
The first jump is a
quad-triple combination.
It should be fine.
He's landed it consistently
during practice.
[gasps]
[KENJIRO]
He nailed it!
[VICTOR] He changed
the triple to a double.
Why is he changing
the jump elements?
Is he going to add a
triple in the second half?
Either that, or he's going
back to attempting three quads.
Completely ignoring the
fact that I told him to focus
on refining the program instead
of getting distracted by jumps.
[VICTOR]
You look too stiff out there!
This is the part that expresses
when I showed up to
be your coach, right?
That look doesn't make it seem
like you were
very happy about it.
[VICTOR]
A triple Salchow.
No, a quad.
He stepped out of the landing.
[VICTOR] I was right--
he did revert the program
to having three quads.
Shake off that last one.
Good.
[VICTOR]
A triple loop.
That was perfect.
[VICTOR]
And now this is Yuri realizing
something like love.
The second half is coming up,
and he already looks tired.
[VICTOR]
An outside spread eagle.
Then an Ina Bauer.
That's right.
Make it so beautiful that no one
can take their eyes off you.
[VICTOR]
A triple axel.
Good, he hung in there.
[VICTOR]
Next up, a triple flip.
[VICTOR] He's not nailing
all of his jumps,
but he's still got
the audience stirred up.
Because of the way his
body moves to the music.
[AUDIENCE claps]
So close!
[VICTOR] He's being too
impatient out there.
But, that's why it is
impossible to look away.
[VICTOR]
Yuri!
I told you to make the last
jump a triple for the points!
[VICTOR chuckles]
[VICTOR] Most skaters
wouldn't rebel against
their coach like he has today.
I wonder who he takes after.
[AUDIENCE claps]
[VICTOR]
I guess that would be me.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[VICTOR] Yakov would have
taken his head off for that,
and I'm tempted
to do it too, but--
Beautiful!
That's a performance
he can be proud of!
Yeah!! Yuri!
[chuckles nervously]
Uh?!
Victor!
Watch the nosebleed!
[ANNOUNCER]
Now the scores for Yuri Katsuki.
His free skate program
score is 165.20,
which makes his total score...
It's amazing you got such
a high score after running
your face into a wall, but
thanks for proving me right
about your ability
to get a solid PCS.
I know you'll do
better next time.
[KENJIRO]
Yuri!
You totally beat me.
But I won't give up, Yuri.
I want to face you in the
Grand Prix series someday.
I hope you won't quit
before I get to!
There's one more thing.
Can I have your autograph?
Yeah, me too!
How about a photo?
Oh, Yuri! I am so proud of you!
You didn't slack off,
even though you were skating
against a bunch of kids!
Still, you scared
the crap outta me
when you slammed
your face into that wall!
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Honestly, I began
the program pretty stiff
because I was so
desperate not to lose.
But somehow... well...
I guess I started having fun.
It's all kind of a blur.
Huh?
[YURI]
It's crazy.
I actually had fun skating
in a competition.
I don't think...
that's ever happened before.
[PLISETSKY grunts]
Geh!
That's quite a temper tantrum.
You saw the photo of Victor and
the Japanese Yuri, didn't you?
Shut your mouth, you hag!
[MOROOKA] Next, we have
recent champion, Yuri Katsuki,
who many believe
will be the next leader
of men's singles in Japan.
Katsuki, if you will.
Um, please, if you'll show
us your theme for this year.
We're dying to know.
I struggled to find a
theme for this Grand Prix.
It was hard, but in the end.
I chose "love."
There have been so many
people who have helped me
in my competitive
skating career.
Yet somehow, I'd never thought
of it as "love" until now.
I was lucky to have
people supporting me,
but I had a hard time
accepting that support.
So I always felt like
I was fighting alone.
But since Victor came into
my life and became my coach.
I've started seeing
things differently.
This "love" isn't something
as clear-cut as romantic love.
It's more of an abstract
feeling that encompasses
my relationships with Victor,
my family, and my hometown.
It took a long time,
but I finally realized that I'm
surrounded by love every day.
For the first time,
there's somebody I want to hold
on to--that person is Victor.
I don't really have
a name for that emotion.
But I've decided
to call it love.
It's changed me.
I'm stronger now.
And I'll prove it
at the Grand Prix Final.
With a gold medal!
We're "abstract"?
What does that even mean?
After all these years,
that's what we get?
The first thing
we're going to do
when he gets back here
is burn that necktie.
It's hideous.
He needs a new one
before the Cup of China.
[CELESTINO]
Victor, if you're hoping Yuri
will win the Cup of China,
you're in for a disappointment.
This year's champion
is Phichit Chulanont.
Did you see how seriously
awesome that jump was?
You were recording it, right?
Uh... No.
Huh?
You were supposed
to get a video, Coach!
I wanted to post it on my page!
[VICTOR]
Dajia hao !
Shanghai crab, please!
[YURI] Victor, you know our
event is in Beijing, right?
[VICTOR]
♪ Crab, crab... ♪
[VICTOR, YURI] ♪ ..shimp,
shrimp, xiao long bao ! ♪
Next time, Sixth Skate:
"China's On!
The Grand Prix Series
Opening Event!
The Cup of China Short Program."