[MOROOKA]
Today we'll see performances
from the six skaters
who survived the brutal
Grand Prix Series to vie
for the coveted title.
And here they are:
[NAOHIKO] In sixth place,
and the last to qualify,
Yuri Katsuki, seeking to redeem
himself in his second Final.
With Victor Nikiforov
as his coach,
he will try to prove
the power of love
by bringing home the gold medal.
Phichit Chulanont finished fifth
in the Grand Prix
Series after becoming
the first Thai skater to win
gold at the Cup of China.
In his first Final,
he's hoping to rewrite history
for Southeast Asian
figure skating.
Yuri Plisetsky came
in fourth in the series.
Last year's junior champion,
this is his senior debut.
He has performed
brilliantly so far,
placing second in both
qualifying events.
As the youngest skater at
this Final, he seeks to defend
Russia's prestige by
securing his first victory.
In third is Christophe
Giacometti of Switzerland.
His mature skating and
giant quadruple Lutz
have enthralled
skating fans worldwide.
He'll be aiming for
his first GP Final gold.
Coming in second
is Otabek Altin,
Kazakhstan's hero.
He won bronze at the World
Championship last season
and claimed his first GP
victory in the NHK Trophy.
His qualification for the Final
this year is another upset.
Finishing first in the
series is Jean-Jacques Leroy,
the man to beat
and the only qualifier
to win both his events.
In his short program and his
free skate, he jumped six quads.
JJ sets a high bar for
his fellow competitors.
Now the moment they've
all been waiting for:
the final round is about
to begin here in Barcelona.
[YURI]
"Gotta Super-Supercharge It!!
Grand Prix Final Short Program."
[MOROOKA]
And now, with the warm-up over,
Yuri Katsuki is the last
skater remaining on the ice.
[VICTOR]
Yuri.
Yes?
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[MOROOKA]
His coach clasps his hand,
displaying the matching
rings that they wear.
Huh? What's with
the matching rings?
--Yuri! Good luck!
--[MICHELE] Good idea!
I wish you and I
had rings like that.
Here I go.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
On the ice...
[MOROOKA] A roaring crowd
greets him as he takes the ice.
--Go, Yuri!
--[MOROOKA] Yuri Katsuki!
--Good luck out there!
You can do it, Yuri!
[MOROOKA] It's hard not to
wonder what's going through
Katsuki's head as he
begins his short program
a year after taking
last place in the Final.
["On Love: Eros" plays]
[MOROOKA] He is skating
to "On Love: Eros."
[MOROOKA] Now, Oda, we've
heard that he's changed
his jump composition
in this program.
[NOBUNARI] Yes, he changed
it after the Rostelecom Cup
for a higher base score.
[YURI] Even if I top my personal
best again, I can't beat JJ.
His program has 5.22
points on mine
in the jumps' base value alone.
I have to take a risk.
You want to switch
it to a quad flip
in your short program?
That's chancy.
You've barely even landed that
jump cleanly in practice.
[YURI] Mm-hm. But I still have
time to improve the execution.
I can't afford complacency,
and finding out
how far I can push myself
will help motivate me
to keep fighting
through the Final.
Don't you wanna
see it, Victor?
Don't you want to see
me land a quad flip
with a plus three GOE?
I do!
Yeah?
[YURI] Since then, I've focused
a lot of practice time
on the quad flip, but my
success rate still isn't high.
I've decided to
go for it, though.
[VICTOR]
Yuri's grown.
He doesn't doubt
his decisions anymore.
But that doesn't change
the fact that my heart
is about to explode.
[NOBUNARI]
A triple axel.
Ha!
[NOBUNARI]
That jump has a difficult entry,
so it will get higher marks.
[MOROOKA] Next up is a
quadruple jump combination.
[NOBUNARI]
Quadruple Salchow,
followed by a triple toe loop.
--Yes!
--[MOROOKA] Another success!
[VICTOR] Excitement
courses through the body,
down to the toes,
and is released!
[MOROOKA] Now, the highly
anticipated quad flip.
[VICTOR]
Good, just use that speed to...
[NOBUNARI] A quadruple flip,
but one hand on the ice.
[MOROOKA] That spin received
a level four rating
--again this season.
--That was so close, Yuri!
That flip had
enough rotation, right?
I'm sure it did.
[LOOP] Dad, hurry,
what's the base value?
[NISHIGORI]
I'm working on it.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[panting]
[YURI panting shakily]
[REPORTER 11A] What do you
have in mind for next season?
[VICTOR]
Hm.
[VICTOR] It was easy enough
to surprise everyone
when I approached each
program like a new beginning.
But constantly starting over
means never building
anything solid.
"I don't need anyone.
I'm strongest on my own."
At least, that's what I thought.
[MOROOKA] All right, here comes
the score for Yuri Katsuki.
Ninety-seven point eight three.
He didn't break
the hundred mark,
but it's still a high score.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[ANNOUNCER 11A] On the ice,
representing Thailand,
Phichit Chulanont.
[VICTOR]
Now it's different.
I can feel a flood
of new emotions
flowing into me through Yuri.
What does he need from me?
What can I give him now?
[MOROOKA] Next is Thailand's
Phichit Chulanont.
["Shall we Skate?" plays]
[MOROOKA] He is skating to
"Shall we Skate?"
A lot of supporters came from
Thailand to cheer him on.
[MOROOKA]
Here comes his first jump.
[NOBUNARI]
A triple axel.
[REPORTER 11A]
Phichit Chulanont is the first
Thai skater to advance
to a Grand Prix Final.
His career began after
his talent was discovered
while he skated at a rink in
the Bangkok commercial district.
He moved by himself to Detroit
to train under Coach Celestino.
Last year, he moved his
home rink back to Thailand.
[NOBUNARI]
Triple Lutz, triple toe loop.
[PHICHIT]
My only quad is the toe loop.
It'll be hard to earn higher
scores than the others.
[NOBUNARI]
A quadruple toe loop.
[PHICHIT] I have no past
accomplishments to defend.
This is my new beginning!
How can I be
anything but excited?
-- Massimo !
--I'm a child
with a blank canvas,
drawing art no one's
ever seen before.
[PHICHIT]
Yuri, I was thinking.
I wanna do a program
to "Shall we Skate?"
The leading actor in the
movie is from Thailand,
but no Thai skater has ever used
the music in a program before.
Someday, though, I'll skate
to it in competition.
And you'll be there,
too. Promise, okay?
[MOROOKA]
That was a flawless performance
--from Phichit Chulanont!
--Bravo!
[panting]
[NOBUNARI]
He seems to be feeling a release
from the intense pressure.
Really, that was amazing.
[YURI]
Good job, Phichit.
You were a perfect
entertainer until the end!
[PLISETSKY grunts]
Get out of the kiss and
cry already, idiots!
Yurio.
Davai .
[MOROOKA] Phichit Chulanont's
score is 95.73.
That's a new personal best.
He is currently in second place.
[ANNOUNCER 11A] On the ice,
representing Russia...
[MOROOKA]
Representing the next generation
of Russian skaters,
--Yuri Plisetsky!
--[MARI] Yurio!
--[MINAKO] Davai ! Davai !
[MOROOKA] He is skating
to "On Love: Agape."
The program was choreographed
by Victor Nikiforov.
["On Love: Agape" plays]
[MOROOKA] Plisetsky has said
that his relative inexperience,
and the resulting nerves,
prevented him from skating
to his full potential
at the Rostelecom Cup.
[MOROOKA]
Here comes his first jump.
[NOBUNARI]
Triple axel.
He used a raised arm,
earning higher marks for
a greater degree of difficulty.
[NOBUNARI]
A flying sit spin.
[MOROOKA]
He won at the Golden Spin,
held right before the Final.
The only thing that Yuri
lacks is experience.
We've provided resources
to help him overcome
that obstacle, and he
has made the most of them.
Agape will be the theme
of his short program.
I believe his interactions
with others in recent months
have helped to refine
his concept of love.
People shine the brightest
when they seek to recognize
and understand what kind
of love sustains them.
[YAKOV]
Vitya...
[MOROOKA] Now, in the
second half of his program,
we'll see a
quad-triple combination.
[NOBUNARI] Quad Salchow,
followed by a triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
That was incredible!
[NOBUNARI]
One arm raised again. Perfect!
[MOROOKA]
His final jump is also a quad.
[NOBUNARI]
A quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
That's it! He did it!
[NOBUNARI]
Both arms raised that time.
[MOROOKA]
All of his jumps were flawless!
[NOBUNARI]
Now the step sequence.
[YURI]
Hm. Where did Victor go?
[MOROOKA] He's attempting
difficult elements
with the highest
possible execution.
Here is a beautiful
ever evolving monster
who continues to go beyond
our highest expectations.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[panting]
[PLISETSKY] Oh, my mind went
blank in the middle of it.
Huh?
Victor--
[MOROOKA] What score will
we see for that performance?
Yuri Plisetsky's score
is 118.56! Amazing!
He's surpassed the world record
set by Victor Nikiforov!
[PLISETSKY]
Oh, yeah, I did it!
[YAKOV]
That's my Yurochka!
[ANNOUNCER 11A] On the ice,
representing Switzerland,
Christophe Giacometti.
[YURI] Um. I wanted to see
how things were going.
[VICTOR]
Chris is about to take the ice.
Let's find a seat.
[YURI]
Okay.
[MOROOKA] The next skater
is Christophe Giacometti
of Switzerland, age 25.
The audience is still
awestruck by Yuri Plisetsky's
new world record, but the arena
is filling with Swiss flags!
["Intoxicated" plays]
[MOROOKA]
He's skating to "Intoxicated."
Giacometti is changing
the mood dramatically,
shifting from agape
to pure lust.
[MOROOKA] He's planned
a high-difficulty quad
for his first jump.
[NOBUNARI]
A quadruple Lutz.
[MOROOKA]
Impressive flow!
[NOBUNARI]
Combination spin.
[MOROOKA] Though he has
advanced to the final
more than once,
Christophe Giacometti
has never won the event.
I wonder how longtime
rival Victor Nikiforov
feels as he watches
Giacometti skate
from his seat in the audience.
[CHRISTOPHE]
Yuri, you're not the only skater
watching from below as
Victor climbed to the top
of the podium all these years.
Given my age, I won't
be competitive enough
to qualify for the
Final much longer.
[meows]
[CHRISTOPHE]
This is the first senior season
I haven't skated against
Victor, and it's been boring.
All right, Chris, ready to go?
You always come too early,
you know that?
[CHRISTOPHE] That's why I'll
make this Final extra special.
[NOBUNARI]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
That was perfect!
[NOBUNARI] The jump's height
and distance were flawless.
[CHRISTOPHE]
Victor, I hope you're watching.
[YURI]
Victor...
Between this and the way
he looked watching Yurio...
[NOBUNARI]
Ooh!
He's done well so far,
but that quad was just
a bit underrotated.
[YURI] His last jump had a flaw,
but Chris is still Chris.
Everything else in his
program had great execution.
He may outscore me.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[CHRISTOPHE]
You should know by now.
I don't give up easily.
[MOROOKA] The score for
Christophe Giacometti is 102.37.
Good job, Chris!
[MOROOKA]
He's passed Yuri Katsuki
and is now in second place.
[BOTH gasp]
Davai !
[ANNOUNCER 11A] On the ice,
representing Kazakhstan.
Otabek Altin.
[MOROOKA] Now we have
Otabek Altin of Kazakhstan.
He finished the Grand
Prix Series in second.
This is his first
trip to the Final.
["Samarkand Overture" plays]
[MOROOKA] He is skating
to "Samarkand Overture."
Altin was the dark horse
of this series,
surprising everyone
with his success.
He is obviously passionate
about winning the gold
for his country.
All right, here comes
his first jump.
[NOBUNARI]
Quadruple toe loop,
triple toe loop!
[MOROOKA]
He nailed it!
[SALA] Before now,
I never thought of Otabek
as a very memorable skater.
Something's different about him.
[MICHELE]
No one had even heard of him
until the junior division.
[COACH 11A] Otabek, what are
you so embarrassed about?
[OTABEK]
I have fewer resources,
and the other talent
was overwhelming.
I have to find something
I can do that they could not,
or else I'd never win.
[OTABEK]
I haven't done ballet since.
There is no one right path.
The ice is a battlefield.
Whatever it takes,
I will survive.
[NOBUNARI]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
Incredible height and distance!
That's what Otabek
Altin is known for.
Here's his last jump.
[NOBUNARI]
A quadruple Salchow.
[MOROOKA]
That had great flow.
Hah.
[YURI] Otabek's jumps
were flawless, too.
There's no hesitation
in his skating.
Determination is very
much his trademark.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[panting]
Somebody else who'll
outscore the piggy.
[YURI whimpers]
He's really talented.
And that program had such flair.
It felt so fresh.
[panting]
Now, go and make us proud.
You get out there and show them.
Show them good, son.
[MOROOKA]
Otabek Altin's score is 112.38.
He beat his personal best again,
and his is now in second place.
[AXEL, LUTZ, LOOP] It's like
a "new personal best" party!
[MOROOKA] Yuri Plisetsky
remains in first place
as the final skater makes
his way onto the ice.
[MOROOKA]
Jean-Jacques Leroy.
A huge group of his supporters
have come here from Canada.
Shouts of "JJ" are
filling the arena.
He is the only
skater who has won
both of his qualifying events.
He is skating to
"Theme of King JJ."
["Theme of King JJ" plays]
[JEAN-JACQUES]
I'm not just going for supremacy
over the Grand Prix Series,
but a grand slam
of the Canadian Nationals,
the Four Continents,
and the World Championship.
Right now, it's
totally within my--
[JEAN-JACQUES gasps]
[NOBUNARI]
Hm, a quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
He'd planned a combination,
but there was only one jump.
[JEAN-JACQUES] Heh. I'll just
turn the quad in the second half
into a combination. No problem!
[NOBUNARI]
Ooh.
It looks like the triple axel
turned into a single.
[ALL]
Oh...
JJ!
Aw, damn it.
He's letting the pressure
of the Final get to him.
[gasps]
After I win at the Worlds,
let's get married.
[gasps] Of course!
[gasps]
[ISABELLA]
And not just the Worlds--
I bet you can win
every single title!
[JJ'S MOM]
Yes, JJ! You can do it!
[JJ'S DAD]
You can win the grand slam!
[yelps]
[screams]
[JEAN-JACQUES]
So this is it.
The pressure of competing
in the Grand Prix Final.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
No!
I won't give up!
I am JJ!
♪ Just follow me! ♪
[JJ FANS]
♪ I will break the walls ♪
♪ Now look at me ♪
♪ Fools will be the,
blind side of the enemy ♪
♪ This is who I am ♪
♪ Just remember me ♪
♪ I'm the king JJ ♪
♪ No one defeats me ♪
♪ This is who I am, baby ♪
♪ Just follow me... ♪
[JEAN-JACQUES]
I can hear you!
All of you!
[MOROOKA]
Next up is his quadruple Lutz.
Let's see how it goes.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Whatever happens,
I'll never stop taking risks.
[MOROOKA] That one turned
into a single as well.
[YURI] It's like seeing
myself from last year.
No, that's not right.
JJ's struggling now
because he took a risk.
No one has the right to mock
the challenge he's taken on.
And I have no regrets for taking
on my own challenge, either.
After all, I've managed to
become one of the final six.
[panting]
[MOROOKA]
All right, now for the score
for Jean-Jacques Leroy.
It's 87.71, the lowest
score he's received
so far in his
senior division career.
[JEAN-JACQUES] I don't
understand. What happened to me?
[ISABELLA]
JJ! JJ! JJ!
[JJ FANS]
[JJ FAN 11A yells]
JJ! JJ! JJ!
Stop!
That's right! It's JJ Style!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
[MOROOKA] The short
programs standings are:
Yuri Plisetsky in first place,
Otabek Altin in second,
and Christophe
Giacometti in third,
with the remaining
rankings as shown.
I'll go for the gold
in my free skate.
[MOROOKA] Yuri Katsuki
will enter the free skate
in fourth place.
That's interesting.
Looks like Minako's
at a bar with Celestino.
Wow, we better stay
away from that place.
Well, anyway, what's up?
You said you wanted to talk.
So?
Right.
[YURI]
After the Final, let's end this.
This is it.
The final event Victor
and I will face together
is about to begin.
[YURI] The eight months
I spent with Victor
were the most intense
in my competitive
figure skating career.
I'm going to skate
my and Victor's love,
laid bare to the world.
Next time, Final Skate:
"Gotta Super-Super-
-Supercharge It!
[YURI, VICTOR]
Grand Prix Final Free Skate."