[YURI]
Hey, guys! Yuri Katsuki here.
The Russian Punk Yurio showed up
to make a play for
my new coach Victor.
Now all hell's broken loose!
Victor is staging
an elaborate face-off
between me and Yurio
called Hot Springs on Ice.
If Yurio wins, Victor will go
back to Russia and be his coach.
But if I win,
Victor will stay here in
Japan and continue as my coach.
So, I'm gonna give it all
the eros I've got in me!
"I Am Eros, and Eros Is Me?
Face-Off! Hot Springs on Ice."
[VICTOR]
First, Yurio's program.
This is "On Love: Agape."
[VICTOR]
Agape. Unconditional love.
Like god's love or a parent's,
infinite, self-sacrificing,
uncalculated.
[YURI]
Aw, man.
This is a tough routine.
Victor can pull
it off beautifully.
But can Yurio do it?
Something like that.
Whatcha think?
Yeah. I got it, no problem.
Huh?
[clapping]
Wow. Really! So beautiful!
Hey. Who said this
chick could watch?
Oh, this is Yuko, one of
the staff here at the ice rink.
I shouldn't have
interrupted your practice,
but it was just so wonderful.
Sorry.
[gasps]
This one's yours,
Yuri, so pay attention!
Yeah. Right!
[YURI] A program
choreographed just for me
by Victor himself!
[VICTOR]
This is "On Love: Eros"
--[YUKO] Guh!!
--[YURI] Ahh!
[VICTOR]
Eros. Sexual love.
Pleasure layered upon pleasure
until you're
drowning in ecstasy.
[YURI]
He's... like sex on ice.
There's so much
eros in this routine,
I think it might impregnate me!
[YURI]
No way!
I can't skate like that!
[VICTOR]
Well?
What do you think?
Oh, I... well, uh...
It was very "eros"!
I know, right?
Now, composition--which quads
do you think you can land?
[YURI]
Well, I can do the toe loop.
And the Salchow in practice,
but I've never landed
it in competition.
Uh... Uh!
But maybe I should
still give it a shot?
What do you think?
Just stick to practicing
your fundamentals for now.
I'll work with Yurio first.
[YURI]
Huh?
I have no intention
of wasting the day trying
to teach you
something you can't do.
How many times have you choked
during a competition, Yuri?
You've shown
you have the skill to win.
Why can't you?
Probably... 'cause I don't have
a whole lot of confidence.
That's right.
What I want to do is help
you find that confidence
and embrace it.
Unleash the eros within you.
Maybe no one's seen it before,
but I know it's there.
Smoldering deep down inside you,
waiting for its
chance to come out.
Can you show it to me?
Can you do that?
You're supposed
to be teaching me
and not chatting with the piggy!
Yeah.
Well, anyway.
[YURI]
Huh?
[VICTOR]
While you're training,
I also expect
you to be thinking.
I want to know
what eros is to you.
[YURI]
Yeah. Sure. No problem.
I can do that.
[AXEL]
Oh...
[LUTZ] I still can't believe we
got a show this big in Hasetsu!
[LOOP] I bet a million
people will show!
And we know what
they're gonna see, don't we?
Yuri kicking butt!
Go, Yuri, go!
Really?
You were stuck
with basic training
because you don't get "eros"?
[YURI]
Yeah.
[NISHIGORI sighs] You shoulda
just made something up.
I bet Victor hasn't thought
about it much either.
Yeah, well, he's a skating god,
so he can get away
with that sort of thing.
You know, thinking
about the program,
I can actually imagine
a story it might be telling.
A handsome, charming
playboy comes to town.
The women fall for
him left and right.
He decides to pursue the most
beautiful one of them all.
But she turns him away.
Undeterred, the man
continues his pursuit
with gifts and
flattery and promises.
Until finally, she gives in.
But, having got what he wanted,
the man loses interest
and moves on to the next town.
Oh, how sexy! Take me now!
Sorry. Good story and all, but
it just doesn't sound like you.
I know!
Anyone who sees it will wish
Victor was the one skating it.
Well, y'know,
you looked kinda sexy
in that video
where you copied him.
[YURI]
I can't just keep copying him!
I mean, I'll never get
better than him that way.
Wait a sec.
You think you can be
better than him someday?
Huh? Oh! No! Of course not!
Let's get real, here.
How many dates
have you had?
You do know he's the
hottest skater in the world?
[laughs]
[VICTOR]
Stop, stop!
Hmm.
Something just doesn't
feel right, here.
But I'm doing
it like you showed me!
[VICTOR]
Hmm...
The way you're
performing it now,
your hunger for
victory is too obvious.
You aren't projecting
the essential purity
that is "agape."
It's good to have confidence.
But in this program, it
shouldn't be front and center.
Yeah?
Far as I can tell,
when you skate,
confidence is always
"front and center."
So how about you tell me
what agape means to you?
It's an emotion,
so why waste time trying to
put it into words, you know?
Right? When you skate,
it's about what
you feel, not what you think.
Haven't you figured
that out yet?
Now, on to the temple!
[PLISETSKY]
The temple?
Nyet ! Ow! Ow!
[sighs]
[YURI]
Damn it.
I'm a man. I'm 23.
I should be able to project
some semblance of sexuality!
Quick favor?
I need a photo of myself in the
bath so I can post it online.
Sorry, we don't let people
take pictures in the bath.
[VICTOR]
Really?
[YURI]
It's no use.
I'm not any closer to
figuring out what eros is.
Eros, eros.
Something that makes
you lose the ability
to make rational decisions.
What does that to me?
What tempts me to act
against my better judgment.
What?
[gasps]
Pork cutlet bowls!
That's it!
That's what eros is to me!
Wow. I'm an idiot.
I take it back.
It's okay.
We can go with that.
It's unique, at least.
Seriously?
[YURI]
Really?
Pork cutlet bowls?
Did I actually say that?
I'm gonna go crawl
under a rock and die!
[VICTOR]
All right!
Imagine the juiciness of the
pork, the softness of the egg.
[YURI]
Got it!
[VICTOR]
You're up, Yurio!
Hmmm... To the temple.
Just tell me what
I'm doing wrong!
Your free leg is looking sloppy.
Keep going!
You can do this!
Yeah.
[VICTOR]
Hmm...
Right! The waterfall!
What now?!
[PLISETSKY]
I'm gonna kill him.
Why am I here too?
This is so stupid.
Really.
I mean, who believes in
unconditional love, anyway?
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY]
Yuratchka.
You were the best one
out there, hands down.
[PLISETSKY]
Thanks, Grandpa.
Do you think you can come
to practice again tomorrow?
I'll skate even better,
you'll see!
I'll be fine,
even if Mom's not there.
[YURI]
Yurio?
Hey, Yurio?
Are you all right?
Why don't we call it a day?
Uh. Okay.
[gasps]
[YURI]
That's weird.
I've never seen him
look so vulnerable.
[PLISETSKY sniffs]
Ugh, where's Victor, anyway?
[YURI] He went to
Nagahama Ramen for dinner.
[PLISETSKY]
Yeah? Then we're going, too!
[YURI]
What?
Vkusno !
[YURI] I can't believe
he still hasn't shown up.
[PLISETSKY] They said he
was drinking until dawn. Stupid.
Oh, Yurio.
[PLISETSKY]
Yeah? 's up?
[YURI] Will you teach me
how to land a quad Salchow?
Please!
[PLISETSKY] You really suck,
Pork Cutlet Bowl.
I'll show you
one more time, okay?
[VICTOR]
Sorry, I'm late!
Hey, there, what were
you practicing just now?
[YURI]
Let's just play this cool.
[PLISETSKY]
Agape. Unconditional love.
To me that means--Grandpa.
Looks like Yurio
finally found his agape.
Maybe he's ready
for the next stage now.
[YURI]
Huh? The next stage?
Do I get a next stage, too,
after I perform the eros
of the pork cutlet bowl?
[YURI]
Except I'm missing something.
The framework of this program
is there, and it's solid,
but I still need
to find its core.
Anyway, what kinda
costumes you wearing?
I have no idea!
I didn't bring anything with me.
I've got ya, don't worry.
I had all my
competition costumes
shipped over from Russia.
[YURI]
Aaaa!
Did he seriously
wear all of this crap?
Wow, this one is
from the Grand Prix Final!
Hey! Don't pick
anything flashier than me!
You wore this at the Junior
Championship, didn't you?
Yeah, I had
long hair at the time,
and my costume was designed
to suggest both male
and female genders.
[YURI]
Yeah,I remember.
I choose this--is that okay?
[door buzzer]
[MINAKO]
You've gotta be kidding me!
Huh?
You do know
what time it is, right?
You wanna practice now?
Sorry it's so late.
But I really need
your help with something!
[MOROOKA]
We're at Ice Castle Hasetsu,
venue of the Hasetsu
Exhibition: Hot Springs on Ice.
I'm here before the face-off to
interview our two competitors:
Yuri Katsuki and Yuri Plisetsky.
You will both be
performing short programs
choreographed for you
by Victor Nikiforov.
Tell us how you are feeling
going into the competition.
Well, you know,
I'm sure looking forward to a
dip in the hot springs after--
[MOROOKA]
You're here to promote yourself,
not the family business!
This sport doesn't
need two Yuris.
I'll crush him.
[MOROOKA]
That's what we want to hear!
Spasibo , spasibo !
And now, last but not least,
let's hear from the architect of
this showdown, Victor Nikiforov!
Hi!
If you've never been to
Hasetsu, you're missing out!
Let's put the
fan down, okay?
[PLISETSKY]
You're making this look like
a cheap publicity stunt!
We're starting soon.
You'd better be ready
to pick a winner!
Today decides which of
us you're going to coach.
[VICTOR]
Right.
I said that, huh?
[PLISETSKY]
You forgot, didn't you?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER A]
Welcome to Hot Springs on Ice,
[MINAKO]
Look at this place!
I can't remember the last time
I saw so many people in here!
[PLISETSKY]
Hmph.
[YUKO]
Yurio!
[PLISETSKY]
Hm?!
You're up in just a minute.
[squeels]
No way!
I remember that costume
from Victor's junior days!
I never thought I would actually
get to see it in person!
It's just so beautiful!
You're gushing
all kinds of fluids
It looks perfect
on you! Good luck!
Spasibo .
[YUKO]
Whoops, you need to go.
Your audience is waiting.
[MOROOKA] He won gold at
the Junior World Championship
and the Junior Grand Prix.
Now he hopes to make
a brilliant senior debut
with a program
by Victor Nikiforov.
It's Yuri Plisetsky!
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[MOROOKA] He will be
skating to "On Love: Agape."
["On Love: Agape" plays]
[MOROOKA]  Here comes his
first jump, a triple axel.
Excellent.
[YURI] He's got everyone
in here mesmerized.
It's different.
This isn't what
I saw in practice.
That moment in the waterfall!
That's when it changed.
[gulps]
[YURI]
He's a beautiful,
ever-evolving monster.
Who can win against that?
[MOROOKA]
Here come the quads
he previously wasn't
allowed to perform.
Daring to put them in the
second half of the program!
A quadruple Salchow,
followed by a triple toe loop.
That's one down and one to go!
[MOROOKA] And here comes
his final jump of the program.
a quadruple toe loop.
And he nails it!
He landed every single jump.
It's hard to believe that
he's only 15 years old!
[PLISETSKY]
Sorry, Grandpa.
I'm too busy concentrating
on the program.
I cannot feel the agape.
[MOROOKA] His signature
move--the combination spin.
[PLISETSKY]
Damn it.
Just end already.
[MOROOKA]
Wow! A masterful performance!
We have a lot to look
forward to this season!
[PLISETSKY]
It wasn't enough.
I'm better than this.
[VICTOR]
Yurio!
That was the best performance
I've seen from you so far!
Go on, take a bow!
[MOROOKA] This young
man truly enthralled
the audience here today.
Yuri Plisetsky!
[YURI]
That was amazing.
He'll definitely rank among
the top senior division skaters.
Oh, God.
If I lose, that means Victor
will go with him back to Russia.
That can't happen.
I have to win.
I have to. I have to.
[VICTOR]
Yuri.
Ready? You're up.
[YURI]
Uh. Yes. I'm ready.
I'm going to skate
with everything
I have out there today.
I'll be the tastiest
pork cutlet bowl ever.
So watch, won't you?
Of course I will.
I love pork cutlet bowls.
Introducing our next skater.
Representing Japan.
A late bloomer who's
become a rising star.
Yuri Katsuki!
[RANDOM FEMALE FAN D]
Good luck, Yuri!
[MOROOKA] He will be
skating to "On Love: Eros."
He struggled with
how to express eros,
but found inspiration
thinking of his favorite dish,
a pork cutlet bowl.
[AUDIENCE whispering]
[MINAKO] After all
the work we did last night,
that is no ordinary
pork cutlet bowl.
["On Love: Eros" plays]
[YURI]
At first I didn't know
who I was dancing for.
But now I do.
[whistles]
[MOROOKA] That step
sequence was pure seduction.
I find it hard to believe he's
imagining a pork cutlet bowl.
[MINAKO]
Good!
Step sequences and spins have
always been your strength.
I want you to teach me
how to move like a woman.
Huh?
[YURI]
I can't be the playboy.
It's not me.
I have to be the beautiful woman
who seduces the playboy.
I won't change any moves.
I'll just change the way I move.
I think that will be
a better expression
of what I really feel.
[MINAKO]
At first I didn't get why
he was so intent on that.
But I see it now.
He's never skated
like this before.
[MOROOKA] Now, we have a spread
eagle right into a triple axel.
[NISHIGORI]
Man, this program is tough.
I wonder if he's
going to regret saving
all the jumps for
the second half.
[MOROOKA]
Whoops!
He stepped out of
that quadruple Sal.
He did stay on his feet,
but his hand touched the ice.
[PLISETSKY]
Yeah, no surprise there.
[YURI]
Don't panic!
Just stay in control.
One mistake doesn't
mean I've lost.
I'm better than any
other woman out there.
And now it's time
to show him why.
[MOROOKA] A quadruple toe loop
followed by a triple toe loop!
Absolute perfection!
[NISHIGORI] A quad-triple
combo at the very end?
Is he insane?
He nailed it, though!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[RANDOM FEMALE FAN F]
Good to see you out there again!
[RANDOM FEMALE FAN G]
Welcome back, Yuri!
It's not "welcome back."
That was a Yuri
we've never seen before.
Nobody could look away.
Something tells me this
will be one hell of a season.
Yuri!
I don't think
I have ever seen
a tastier or more
inspiring pork cutlet bowl!
[YURI]
Really? That means a lot.
And now, there's
something I want to ask you.
Okay. Sure.
What was with that
pathetic triple axel out of
the spread eagle? And I guess
your quad Salchow is better,
but obviously Yurio didn't
teach you well enough in
your secret practice sessions.
Uh, Yuri?
Where are you going? Hey!
[YUKO] You're leaving without
even hearing the results?
I already know
what the results are.
That performance.
I'll keep skating under Yakov.
Dasvidaniya .
I'm sorry.
This isn't over, though.
I'm taking gold at
the Grand Prix Final.
Tell him that.
[MOROOKA]
It's official!
Yuri Katsuki is the winner
of Hot Springs on Ice!
Well done!
Do you have any words
for the audience?
I... Um... Well...
[gasps]
This was the beginning.
With Victor, I hope
to win the Grand Prix Final.
Thank you all for
your continued support!
[MINAKO sobs]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[YURI]
Here we go.
The battle for my figure
skating career has begun!
[YURI] I really don't think
there's anyone who'd want
to see me naked on the ice.
[VICTOR]
Don't be so sure!
At the very least, I would.
[YURI]
Huh?
[VICTOR]
Fourth Skate: "Like Yourself.
[VICTOR, YURI]
And Complete the Free Program!"