[YURI]
After the Final, let's end this.
What?
You've already done
more than enough for me,
more than I could've dreamed of.
My final season was
my best one yet.
That's because of you.
Thank you for
everything, so much.
Thank you for being my coach.
[YURI gasps]
Victor?
[VICTOR]
Damn it.
That's disappointing.
I didn't expect this
from you of all people.
Something so selfish.
[YURI] Selfish or not,
it's my decision. I'm retiring.
Yes, Yuri? What are
you looking at?
[YURI] Um, I'm just
surprised to see you cry.
I'm mad, okay? What should I do?
You're the one who said
it was only until
the Grand Prix Final!
[VICTOR] I thought you'd
eventually decide
you wanted my help
for longer than that.
It's okay.
You don't need
to worry about me.
This way you can
make your comeback--
Stop! I don't want to hear it!
How can you tell me
to return to the ice
when you're retiring?
[YURI]
We decided that we would each
make our own decision after
the free skate was over.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[NAOHIKO] Welcome to the Grand
Prix of Figure Skating Final.
Tonight, we'll
have our champion.
In first is Russia's
Yuri Plisetsky,
with the highest ever
short program score.
Otabek Altin,
hero of Kazakhstan,
is ranked second in his
first Grand Prix Final.
Christophe Giacometti
of Switzerland
is in third after a very
distinct performance.
Yuri Katsuki hopes
to turn fourth place
into a spot on the podium.
Phichit Chulanont,
the first Thai skater
to qualify for the
Final, is in fifth.
And, shockingly,
Jean-Jacques Leroy of Canada
enters the free skate in sixth.
Will he make a comeback?
The last chapter of
the Grand Prix Final
is about to begin.
This is Stéphane Lambiel
reporting from Barcelona.
Now over to Morooka.
Thank you, Morooka here.
Japan's Yuri Katsuki has
not practiced publicly
since the day after
the short program.
His supporters have been
concerned by his sudden
and unexplained disappearance.
But he did return to the ice for
this morning's public practice.
[STEPHANE]
Salut , Victor!
Oh, salut , Stéphane.
It's been a while.
Good to see you again.
We hope Yuri's supporters will
cheer loudly for him today.
[STEPHANE]
I'm sure they will.
Thanks for speaking
with us. Bon Chance .
I have to say, neither Yuri
Katsuki nor his coach Victor
seem to have the energy we've
come to expect from them.
[YURI] "Gotta Super-Super-
-Supercharge It!!!
Grand Prix Final Free Skate."
[MOROOKA] The Men's Singles
Free Skate is about to begin.
First on the ice is
Jean-Jacques Leroy of Canada.
He is far behind after
a series of mistakes
in his short program.
["Partizan Hope" plays]
JJ, the music started!
[gasps]
[JEAN-JACQUES]
I can't believe I just did that.
I've been skating for 16 years.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Mom! Dad!
Did you see me?
[JEAN-JACQUES]
And now I suddenly feel like
I've been tossed onto
the ice for the first time.
--[AUDIENCE cheers]
--[JEAN-JACQUES grunts]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Looks like
he didn't enter the jump
with enough speed.
[MOROOKA] That jump was
Jean-Jacques Leroy's specialty.
His practice was
full of mistakes, too.
Still, he is the sole
skater among the final six
with four quads in his program.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Quadruple
toe loop, triple toe loop.
--Good job, son!
--[MOROOKA] Nailed that one!
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Leave me alone!
[JJ'S MOM]
JJ?
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Mom. I'm sorry.
It's just that... I'm so lost!
I don't know what to do!
[JEAN-JACQUES] I'd never
been that angry before.
I feel like a bird
with a broken wing.
[AUDIENCE applauds]
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Stop it!
I don't deserve your
applause right now!
Given the current totals,
I might be able to claw
my way onto the podium
if some of the others mess up.
But come on, me,
win out of sheer luck?
That's not how I do things!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[ISABELLA gasps]
[MOROOKA]
Another success!
I don't care what score he gets.
When he comes of the ice,
we're gonna show him
nothin' but a smile.
It's something I call JJ Style.
Listen, Coach, I--
The only word I want
to hear from you is "yes."
[JEAN-JACQUES] Whatever else
happens, JJ will stay JJ.
Just watch me!
[MOROOKA]
For his final jump,
he's planned a
quadruple toe loop.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
A plan is just a plan!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple loop!
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Yes!
[MOROOKA]
That's Jean-Jacques Leroy!
He rose to the challenge!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] He stepped
out of it, but overall,
a great jump.
What?
I guess he has done
it during practice.
JJ landed a quad loop, huh?
The Four Continents
just got a lot more fun.
[YURI] Even if mine ends here,
their battles will continue
for years after this
Grand Prix Final.
No tale is more compelling
than one that never ends.
[MOROOKA] Jean-Jacques Leroy
of Canada scores 213.91.
A high score right of the bat!
JJ hasn't changed
at all over the years.
A pupil's accomplishment
is headier
than any wine could ever be.
Phichit, use your performance
to intoxicate the world.
["Terra Incognita" plays]
[MOROOKA]
In his short program,
Phichit Chulanont
of Thailand, age 20,
bewitched the audience
here in Spain.
His supporters back home have
high expectations, as well.
[PHICHIT]
I've never had such a big crowd
cheering for me before.
I wanna turn in a
flawless performance.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA] He stumbled but
got back up immediately.
[PHICHIT]
I have to keep them entertained!
Jiayou !
[PHICHIT] So far, the
toe loop is my only quad.
I'll add more to my roster
eventually, but for now--
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA] Looks like
his nerves have settled!
[PHICHIT]
I may only have one quad,
but I know that my
skating stands out
from every other
skater competing here!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Triple flip,
single loop, double flip.
[MOROOKA] He landed his
last jump combination!
[PHICHIT]
There's this dream I have.
I haven't even told
Yuri about it yet.
But, someday, I wanna have
an ice show in Thailand.
I want everyone
back home to know
how much fun figure skating is!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[YURI] Victor, will you be
my coach until I retire?
[VICTOR] In that case,
I hope you never retire.
[YURI] Let's win gold together
at the Grand Prix Final.
Don't worry,
you can win the gold.
Just skate your best.
Believe in yourself.
[YURI]
Hey, Victor.
I told you before.
All I want is for you
to be who you are.
So don't suddenly start trying
to sound like a coach now.
[gasps]
[YURI] I want to smile for
my last time on the ice.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The score for Phichit Chulanont
is two 289.56.
Yuri, listen to me.
I debated whether I should
say this to you now, but...
I took a break after becoming
the five-time world
champion to coach you,
so how is it possible that you
still haven't won a gold medal?
[VICTOR]
How much longer
are you going to stay
in warm-up mode?
I really want to
kiss that gold medal.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
On the ice, representing Japan,
Yuri Katsuki.
[MOROOKA]
What's going on?
Skater Katsuki looks like
he might be crying.
[YURI]
Right. I know what my goal is.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
Good luck!
[AXEL, LUTZ, LOOP]
Go, Yuri!
He better hurry.
He's running out of time.
[YURI]
My name is Yuri Katsuki.
At 24, I'm one of the
dime-a-dozen figure skaters
certified by the JSF.
["Yuri on Ice" plays]
[MOROOKA] Katsuki says he
wants to use this program
to express the different
forms of love he feels.
He is skating to "Yuri on Ice."
[MOROOKA] All right, he's
planned two consecutive quads.
The first is part
of a combination.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Quadruple toe loop,
double toe loop.
[YURI] I've spent more than
half my life watching Victor,
trying to catch up.
And now, thanks
to him, here I am.
[YURI]
Well, not just him.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Salchow.
He's a different
skater than the one
who first learned
that jump from Yurio.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple flip.
[VICTOR] He changed it
from the triple toe loop.
Yuri, what are you doing?
[YURI] My performance needs
to be better than flawless
for a chance at the gold.
I've been thinking ever
since the short program.
I would like for the final
free skate of my career
to have the same
difficulty as Victor's.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA] He has a
triple flip planned next.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop?
[VICTOR]
A quad?
You added it to bring
the total up to four?
[YURI]
Do you realize it now, Victor?
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Triple axel,
single loop, triple Salchow.
[YURI]
I don't want it to end here.
I wanna skate with you forever.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Triple Lutz, triple toe loop.
[YURI] But the price of
keeping you as my coach
would be slowly killing you
as a competitive skater.
Look at the Victor
who lives on inside me.
Becoming my coach
wasn't a waste of time.
I'm the only one
who can prove it,
and that's what I'm doing now.
[MOROOKA] The last jump is
a quad, the signature move
of his coach, Victor Nikiforov!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple flip.
[MOROOKA]
He did it!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[panting]
[MOROOKA]
Yuri Katsuki has delivered
a masterful performance
here today,
one that may well be the
culmination of his career!
[SARA, MIRA, EMIL cheering]
[VICTOR]
Yuri!
[YURI] I don't wanna go
to the kiss and cry.
Going back there
means it's over.
[VICTOR]
Don't look so worried.
Your performance was
basically perfect.
It'll be a very high score.
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
The score for Yuri Katsuki...
[MOROOKA]
We have Yuri Katsuki's scores.
Incredible!
His free skate score is 221.58.
He's broken the world record for
the Men's Singles Free Skate,
long held by none other than
his own coach Victor Nikiforov.
His combined score is 319.41.
He's jumped all the
way to first place!
[VICTOR]
Congratulations, Yuri.
Now both Yuris have
beaten my world records.
That is the ultimate compliment
as your choreographer and coach.
But, the ultimate affront
as your fellow competitor.
Wait. You mean...
You're coming back?
[ANNOUNCER 11A]
On the ice...
[CHRISTOPHE]
The guy rumored to be retiring
banged out a world record.
Talk about a happy ending.
["Rapsodie Espagnole" plays]
[MOROOKA] Christophe
Giacometti is skating to
"Rapsodie Espagnole."
[CHRISTOPHE] I thought
this Grand Prix Final
would be my chance to win,
maybe even the last
chance I'll have.
But Yuri handily beat
my personal best.
Looks like it isn't
going to be easy
to get my hands on a medal.
But I still mean to enjoy
this final until the very end.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Lutz!
[CHRISTOPHE]
I can do this.
[VICTOR]
Yay!
Will you get a photo
of us with this one, too?
[gasps, grumbles]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] He'd planned
a quadruple Salchow,
but it became a single.
Come on! Hang in there, Chris!
[BOTH]
Allez !
Go, Chris!
[gasps]
[CHRISTOPHE]
Victor.
I got too used to having
you in front of me.
I pretended not to feel
the disappointment
of always being surpassed.
But maybe it's time to
fan the flames of regret.
There!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
Hold on, a lone triple axel?
He changed it to make
a jump combination
in the second half.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Triple axel,
single loop, triple Salchow.
[MOROOKA]
His final jumps were successful!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Yes.
He brought a combination
he usually does
in the first half into
the second instead.
[MOROOKA] They're giving
him a standing ovation.
The audience loves him!
[CHRISTOPHE moans]
[CHRISTOPHE pants]
I love you!
Over here!
Huh?
Merci.
[MINAKO, FNAGIRLS squeal]
[MOROOKA]
His free skate score is 188.32,
making his total score 290.69.
After four skaters,
he is in third place.
Yuri Katsuki,
currently in first,
is guaranteed a spot
on the podium.
Altin finished the short program
6.18 points behind
Yuri Plisetsky.
He takes the ice now to fight
for a place on the podium
at his first Grand Prix Final.
All right, Otabek. Good luck.
["Symphony No.9" plays]
[MOROOKA] He is skating
to the second movement
from Beethoven's
"Symphony No.9."
[OTABEK] Now is the time
for you to take center stage.
The whole world
is waiting for you.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
He landed it.
[VICTOR]
Yakov!
Have a sec? Can we talk?
Not right now. Find me later.
Yuri's about to go on the ice.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Quadruple
Salchow, triple toe loop.
You what?! You're coming back?
Yes.
I'll time my return to
the Russian Nationals.
Wait, does this mean
the pork cutlet bowl's
going to retire?
Well, that is
entirely up to him.
He said he was going to make
his decision after the Final.
[gasps]
[OTABEK] Don't let yourself
lose sight of what you want.
Now is the time to take off.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[OTABEK]
Fulfill your dream.
Only you can make it a reality.
Live your life as it
was meant to be lived.
Hey, where'd Victor go?
[gasps]
[OTABEK]
Move. Dance your dream.
Sing. Sing.
Sing your own song.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Salchow.
[MOROOKA]
That was his last quad.
He landed them all!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Triple flip,
single loop, triple Salchow.
Amazing.
Talent and originality
aren't only about
what you're born with.
Some things you get by fighting.
At 19, he's about to prove that.
[OTABEK]
Work to the fullest.
Play to the fullest.
Discover all you can.
Follow your own path until
it ends, and then keep going.
Now is the beginning.
Now is your chance to live.
[MOROOKA]
Here comes his final jump.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple loop.
[MOROOKA] All of his
jumps were successful!
[gasps]
Oh, wow!
[OTABEK] This is your beginning.
This is your time.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[panting]
[MOROOKA] Otabek Altin
missed Jean-Jacques Leroy
by a sliver and is
currently in third!
Katsuki remains in first place.
The final skater to take the ice
is 15-year-old Yuri
Plisetsky of Russia.
[YURI]
Yuri, davai !
[PLISETSKY]
Yakov, Lilia,
Grandpa, Yuko,
and, Yuri Katsuki, watch this.
["Allegro Appassionato
in B Minor" plays]
[MOROOKA]
He is skating to
"Allegro Appassionato
in B Minor."
Young as he is, Yuri Plisetsky
set a new world record
with his short program.
If he wins the Grand Prix
Final in his senior debut,
it will make men's
singles history.
First up is a quad.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Salchow.
[MOROOKA]
He nailed it!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A spiral into...
...a triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
Another success!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
That was a difficult entry,
he used a raised arm
during the jump,
earning higher marks
for greater difficulty.
[PLISETSKY]
Yuri Katsuki.
He screws up his jumps, but his
step sequence is impressive.
I want to see him skate
with no mistakes.
What kind of guy is he?
He's crying? What a loser.
We don't need two Yuris
in the same bracket.
Time for you to retire.
Loser!
[PLISETSKY] What, you're going
to retire once you win gold?
You don't care anymore
now that you've
beat Victor's high
score? That's bull!
Don't disappoint me!
They don't give
gold medals to pigs!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple flip.
[YURI]
Hang in there, Yurio.
Here come the second-half jumps.
[PLISETSKY]
I'm going to win!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
A big fall there!
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
He got up right away,
into a beautiful
spiral position.
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY] Yurochka,
you've become so strong.
[LILIA] You're no longer
a prima ballerina.
You've evolved into
something new and beautiful
all your own. Well done, Yuri.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Quadruple
Salchow, triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
Brilliant execution!
Both arms raised again.
He is pushing himself hard.
[PLISETSKY]
Well, Yuri Katsuki,
are you watching?
You set a new record, but I'm
going to beat it someday.
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Quadruple
toe loop, double toe loop.
[MOROOKA] Adding a quad at
this point in the program?
[PLISETSKY] If you retire now,
I'll make you regret it
for the rest of your life.
Loser!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Triple axel,
single loop, double Salchow.
[MOROOKA]
Incredible!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[panting]
[MOROOKA] Yuri Plisetsky's
free skate score is 200.97.
His combined score
is 0.12 points
higher than Yuri Katsuki's.
He takes gold with
a razor-thin margin!
[MOROOKA] Yuri Katsuki
makes it to the podium
for the first time.
[STÉPHANE] Oui, and what
a magnificent result.
He gave us an
extraordinary performance,
one that nobody
would have expected
after last year's Final.
Well, it's not
a gold medal, but...
That's nice, but I'm not
going to kiss your medal
unless it's gold. Sorry!
Aw, I was really looking forward
to kissing that gold medal!
How can I ever recover
from my failure as a coach?
You wouldn't have any
suggestions, would you, Yuri?
Something that might excite me?
[gasps]
[VICTOR]
Well, anything come to mind?
Oh, well, uh...
I, uh--
Victor!
I want to stay in
competition with you
for one more year.
And this time I'll win gold!
[gasps]
Perfect! Well, almost.
Huh?
[VICTOR chuckles] Even for me,
it's not going to be easy
to make a full comeback
while also staying
on as your coach.
In exchange, I expect
five world championships
at the very least.
[YURI sniffles]
'Kay.
[MOROOKA] The is silver
medalist, Yuri Katsuki of Japan.
His exhibition is a free program
previously performed
by his coach.
Victor Nikiforov has just
announced his own comeback.
This is last year's
"Stay Close to Me."
["Stay Close to Me" playing]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[YURI panting]
[YURI] There's a place
you just can't reach
unless you have a dream that's
too large to bear alone.
Win or lose, we call
everything on the ice "love."
[VICTOR]
Yuri!