[YURI groans]
[screams]
[whines]
[YURI pants]
I'm so sorry!
I overslept! Um... are you?
Well, Good morning, Yuri!
I have to say, you
are impressively late.
Only Aeroflot has kept
me waiting longer.
Oh, how fun!
Japanese dogeza !
[YURI] Since I beat
Yurio in the face-off,
Victor will be staying
in Hasetsu to train me.
To me, it's more like having
a god around than a coach.
This whole experience
has been surreal.
I mean, I'm going to have
a coach of my very own
here with me every day.
And not just any
coach--Victor Nikiforov!
I guess it's good that he said
I could pay his
coaching fees later,
but... I still don't know
how I'm gonna do that.
[YURI grunts]
I've noticed you
tend to flub your jumps
when there's
something on your mind.
Care to share?
[YURI]
"Like Yourself...
And Complete the Free Program!!"
[VICTOR]
I've been thinking.
I wonder if three quads in
your free program is too many.
Why?
Uh... If I want to win
the Grand Prix Final,
I need to keep those jumps in!
Not true.
You can get by
with just one quad.
Just get a perfect score
on the program components,
and you're good to go!
[photo snap]
[YURI] Let me pause here to
explain how scoring works
in figure skating.
Jumps and spins count
toward a technical score.
Choreography and
interpretation count toward
presentation score.
The skater's total score
is the sum of those two,
minus any deductions.
When I skate,
I tend to get nervous
and lose technical points
by missing jumps.
I usually make up ground
with my presentation score,
but it's not always enough.
I need to do more.
I'll never win this way.
Something has to change.
[VICTOR]
Yuri, you know why I'm here,
why I decided to
become your coach?
[YURI]
Huh?
[VICTOR]
I was drawn to you
because of the way
you move to the music.
Like the song's
already inside you
and you're using
your body to release it.
You need a
high-difficulty program
to maximize that potential.
I knew, I could give you that.
And the short program
confirmed that I was right!
Now we're moving on
to the free program.
And I think you should
produce this one yourself.
Huh? But my coach has always
chosen my music for me.
I wouldn't know where to start--
[VICTOR]
It's more fun to do it yourself.
You can really personalize it!
[YURI] Anyway, I'm used
to my coach doing it.
[VICTOR]
Who was your last coach again?
[OLD MAN A]
Thank you, God. Thank you.
[VICTOR, YURI]
Hmm?
[CELESTINO]
Yuri?
Ciao, ciao!
It's been a while Since
the Grand Prix Final, yes?
Yeah, I guess it
has been a long time.
[CELESTINO] I hear Victor
is coaching you now.
He is. I'm really sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
[VICTOR]
Ciao, ciao! Celestino!
This is Victor, Yuri's coach.
You having fun playing coach?
You're not getting tired of it?
Hey, I was wondering.
Why didn't you ever let
Yuri choose his program music?
[CELESTINO]
Huh?
I usually select the
music for my skaters.
But I don't mind letting them
chose if that's what they want.
Yuri only brought me a piece
once while I was coaching him.
I think he'd had a
friend of his compose it.
It wasn't bad,
the song was okay...
So this is the music
that's going to get you a win?
[YURI]
Uh...
You know, maybe you should
pick something for me.
He just never had much
confidence in himself
or his decisions.
I told him a million times
to trust himself more,
but I don't think
it ever helped.
That's good to know, thank you.
Um, hold on.
Celestino, one more thing.
At the next Grand Prix Final,
I'm going to make you proud.
Hmm. I'm glad to hear that.
It's what I was hoping you would
say after last year's final.
[sighs]
That's a load off.
I couldn't bring myself
to call him for so long.
[VICTOR]
Yuri, I think it's about time
I heard this music he mentioned.
Yeah, okay.
Why didn't you
tell me about it before?
I'm your coach, aren't I?
I should have.
I'm sorry.
[PLISETSKY]
Huh?
The little piggy's producing
his own free program?
[YUKO]
Hey, Yuri!
I hope things are
good in Russia.
Have you worked out
your free program yet?
I'm looking forward
to seeing it!
What's she doing, scouting out
the competition for her buddy?
His own program?
Seems ballsy for him.
[MIRA]
Oh?
Is this why you went to Japan,
to find yourself a girl?
Get off me.
You don't know what
you're talking about, Mira.
Are you throwing yourself at me
because you dumped
that hockey player?
'Cause I'm not interested.
I wouldn't risk getting
killed by a jealous meathead
just to go out with you.
Nyet !
Did I mention I've been
practicing my lifts lately?
Let me down, hag!
Hey, I'm only three years
older than you are.
What are you children up to?
Hello, Coach Yakov.
[YAKOV] Are the two of you
switching to pairs' skating?
No. Sorry, sir.
[MIRA] Yuri seems different
since he got back.
I wonder why.
He used to complain
about practice.
There was no one in his
bracket who could rival him.
He knew that and
it made him arrogant
and unwilling to work hard.
I think that face-off
with Yuri Katsuki
was a wake-up call for him.
We may have a very
interesting season ahead of us.
Oh my god, look!
Huh?
[MOM A]
It's Lilia Baranovskaya!
[MOM B] Former prima ballerina
of the Bolshoi Ballet!
Thank you taking time
out of your busy schedule.
[LILIA]
Which one is he?
If I don't like what
I see, I'm leaving.
Aw, man.
Who's this ved'ma ?
[LILIA]
Good teeth, at least.
Not very flexible, is he?
We'll start from
square one with ballet
Whatever you say.
Who the hell are you?
[LILIA] The person
choreographing
your free program.
That's right.
And my expectations
for you are high.
You will be more than
a principal this season.
Yes, you will be
the prima ballerina.
If you want to win, you must
be willing to sell your soul.
[MIRA]
Well, she's intense.
I want victory, whatever
the cost might be.
If it means winning, then I will
sell my body and soul to you.
[LILIA]
Hmph.
I am Lilia Baranovskaya.
I want you to go home
and pack up your things.
We have a great deal
of work to do,
so you'll be staying with me.
So will you, Yakov.
[YAKOV]
Lilia!
[LILIA]
Don't get excited, old man.
This doesn't mean we're
getting back together.
[YAKOV] No! That's not
what I was aiming for.
I don't really get why,
but for some reason
Yurio's coach brought in his
ex-wife to help with training,
and apparently she yells
at him like 24 hours a day.
[YURI] Yeah?
That doesn't sound like fun.
Anyway, have you
chosen the music
for your free program yet?
[YURI] Well, I did
have Victor listen to one.
Oh, okay.
So this is it, huh?
[YURI]
He wasn't exactly a fan.
Let's consider some
other possibilities, huh?
[YURI] Usually, I would
just let my coach pick
whatever music he
thought was best.
And then I'd let him
choreograph it, too.
Not Victor.
He did it all himself.
He'd have new music written
to create the story he wanted
to tell and then choreograph
his routine to tell it.
I did dream about doing
that myself someday,
but it just never happened.
[YURI]
Hmm...
Oh... How's Phichit?
He's practicing back
home in Thailand.
[YURI]
Uh. Hey, Phichit.
Sawasdee krab .
What's up, Yuri?
It's been a long time.
Good to hear from you!
So I guess you
left Detroit behind
to go practice back
in Thailand, huh?
Sure did. What can I say?
Detroit just wasn't
the same after you left.
You should come visit me
in Bangkok sometime.
I'll show you around.
[YURI laughs]
Khob khun , krap .
Anyway, I was wondering,
think you could do me a favor?
You remember that
demo I had made?
Yeah.
By that one
conservatory student.
You asked her to compose
it for you, right?
[YURI]
Uh-huh.
But then I didn't
end up using it after all.
Sorry.
I know you went
to a lot of trouble.
[CONSERVATORY GIRL]
No, it's all right.
Just keep it.
Sorry again.
Anyway.
It felt kind of awkward
to talk to her after that.
[PHICHIT]
Yeah.
I can see why.
If you want, I could try
to track her down for you.
I'm sure she's not mad.
[YURI] The piece never
did feel quite right.
I always thought there was
something weak about it.
Though I guess that makes sense.
When I asked her to compose it,
I said I was looking for
something to represent me,
something that would embody
my skating career as a whole.
[YURI] So I guess she
got it right in the end.
An underwhelming piece
for an underwhelming career.
[YURI] What should
I have done differently?
[LILIA]
No, no, no!
Forget who you were!
Your past self
is dead, understand?
The only people who succeed
are those who are
willing to be reborn
as many times as necessary!
[VICTOR] What? You still
haven't chosen the music?
Trust your intuition.
Find something
that inspires you.
It could even be a memory.
Like when a girl
said she loved you.
What?!
Huh? I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to snap at you.
I'm just really
stressed right now.
[VICTOR]
No. It's my fault.
I forgot you've
never had a lover.
Yuri! Why don't
we go get some food?
I'm okay, thanks.
Yuri! Want to soak
in the springs together?
I'm going to sleep.
[VICTOR] Yuri!
How about a slumber party?
I can't do it!
The guilt's gonna kill me!
Let's skip practice today.
We can go down to the ocean.
[trembles]
Yeah, okay.
[VICTOR]
Ah. Seagulls.
[YURI]
Black-tailed gulls.
I love the sound they make.
Whenever I hear
their calls in the morning,
it makes me think
I'm back in St. Petersburg.
I never thought
I would leave the city,
so I didn't take the time to
appreciate the seagulls' cries.
But now I find them
strangely comforting.
Have you ever
felt like that before?
[YURI]
Back in Detroit,
there was this girl who
was really pushy,
always talking to me and
asking how I was doing.
Then one day a rink
mate had an accident.
I was worried.
Really worried.
That girl was in the hospital
waiting room with me.
She tried to give me a hug,
you know, to comfort me.
But I just reflexively
shoved her away.
Wow. Why would you do that?
[YURI] It felt like
she was trying to say
I was weak or something.
She was intruding on feelings
she didn't have any right to.
And I hated it.
That made me think
about everyone back home.
Minako, Yuko,
Nishigori, my family.
They never treated me
like I was a weakling,
someone who needed
his hand held.
They had faith that
I would continue to grow,
and they let me do it,
helping me without ever
making me feel weak.
You aren't a weak person, Yuri.
Nobody who knows you
would ever think that.
Will you tell me: What is
it you want me to be to you?
A father figure?
[YURI]
No.
A brother?
Or just a friend?
[YURI]
Hmmm...
[VICTOR]
So, then, your lover.
I can try my best.
No, no, no, no, no!
All I want is for you
to be who you are.
[YURI]
I look up to you.
I always have.
I was afraid to let
you see my shortcomings.
I guess that's why
I've been avoiding you.
I'll make it up to you
by skating my best.
You have a deal.
And I won't let you off easy.
That's my way of
showing my love.
[YURI] When I open up,
he meets me halfway.
[YURI] I think it's time
to open up more.
[YURI sighs]
Huh?!
[YURI]
I heard back.
She said she's going
to redo the music!
[VICTOR]
Sounds good.
Looking forward to hearing it.
[YURI]
Until it's ready, um...
I want to learn all your jumps!
Teach me everything you can do.
Absolutely unacceptable.
Even the king crab we ate
yesterday had better control
of its legs than you!
Again, from the same place.
Well?
Ma'am!
[YAKOV]
It might be for the best
that he's not training in
Victor's shadow anymore.
He's learning that
strength isn't only
about how confident you appear.
[YURI]
That was good.
If it's all right with you, I'd
like to try it one more time.
Uh, we've done it ten
thousand times already.
[YURI]
Thirteen, actually.
[VICTOR]
I've thought this for a while,
but your stamina is
pretty impressive.
[YURI]
Yeah. I've got that, at least.
[VICTOR] Maybe your nervous
eating during competitions
helps keep you going longer.
There's also the fact that you
haven't had any major injuries,
and you're younger than me.
Uh!! I just couldn't help it!
Sorry!
[VICTOR]
Is it getting that thin?
No, no, no, no!
It's very thick and shiny!
[VICTOR]
You've wounded me.
I don't know if
I will ever recover.
[YURI] I'm sorry, I don't
know what I was thinking!
I didn't mean anything by it...
[NISHIGORI] Well, those two seem
to get along pretty well, huh?
[YUKO chuckles]
[YURI]
It's here!
Victor! Listen!
[MAKKACHIN yelps]
[YURI]
Oops, sorry!
It's the music for
the free program!
[VICTOR] Hmm... We could
go for a bit more impact.
Maybe make the last jump
a quadruple toe loop.
[YURI]
Really? The last one?
[VICTOR] I think someone
with your stamina
should be able to pull it off.
But if you'd rather not.
I'll do it!
Good. That's what I was
hoping you would say.
Oh, yeah. One more thing.
Did you change
the musical theme?
Uh, yeah, I did.
[VICTOR]
So, what is it?
I've decided--the piece's
theme is "on my love."
I think that's a perfect choice.
Well done.
Okay. Let's finish this program!
[YURI]
Yeah!
[MINAKO]
No way!
Yes! They announced them!
This year's assignments
for the Grand Prix!
Oh, crap! Oh, crap! Oh, crap!
What are you doing up?
Do you have any
idea what time it is?
Mom, the assignments!
Oh crap! Oh crap!
[YAKOV]
Yuri!
Where is he?
The assignments are in!
[PLISETSKY] First I want
to know, the Japanese piggy:
Where is he assigned?
Congratulations, Yuri!
Hooray! Yay!
Thanks, everybody.
Now we can take a closer look
at the events you'll
be competing in.
Hold on a second!
Somehow the Katsuki
family still doesn't know
how figure skating works.
[LOOP]
So how about a quick tutorial?
[HIROKO]
Thank you.
That would be helpful, dear.
What is the Figure
Skating Grand Prix Series?
Skaters with high scores
from the previous season
participate in a maximum
of two competitions
out of a total of six worldwide.
Only the top six skaters
from those meets
advance to the
Grand Prix Final,
which determines
who is number one.
They announced
who will be competing
and this year Yuri's first
assignment is the third event,
the Cup of China.
Yuri's former rink mate,
Phichit of Thailand,
will be competing too!
Ah! It'll be good to see him!
And it looks like
his second assignment
is going to be.
The sixth event,
Russia's Rostelecom Cup.
where he'll be up against his
arch nemesis, Yuri Plisetzky!
Go, Yurio, go!
[YURI]
So I'll be going against him
even before the final.
[MAKKACHIN whines]
I trust you'll
look after the house
during the season
for us, Makkachin?
[YURI]
That's right.
This will be my first time
in a Grand Prix Series
without Victor in the lineup.
I wonder how people
are gonna react
when they see you.
Showing up with
Victor as your coach,
they'll probably think you
stole him from the sport.
[YUKO]
You'll be hated
by millions of skating
fans worldwide!
Uh...
[YUKO]
Just kidding!
We're totally on
your side, Yuri!
[MINAKO]
Hell yeah, we are!
I'll be there to cheer
you on this season, too!
First stop, Cup of China.
Here we come!
Wait a second.
Nationals last year.
Yeah, I forgot about that.
I wish I could forget.
I screwed up and
came in eleventh.
Okay.
So you have to compete in
the block championships.
What are those?
Oh, we're talking about
domestic competitions now.
[photo snap]
[YUKO] Yuri had a major loss
in last year's National's.
That means
he won't automatically
make the cut for this season's
championship and has to work
his way up from qualifying
competitions instead.
So his first event this season
is the regional competition
for Chugoku, Shikoku,
and Kyushu in September.
It'll be his big comeback!
Great. You'll breeze
through that, won't you?
Well, Minami from
Fukuoka will be there.
[LOOP] Yeah. He beat
Yuri in the Nationals.
[LUTZ] Minami Kenjiro of
Kyushu said to be the number one
rising star among
younger skaters.
September.
[YURI] Hard to believe
it's already been so long
since the day
I thought I was finished.
[TOSHIYA]
Good, good.
So exciting.
We'll be there
to cheer you on!
I'm sure you'll do great.
Thanks a lot, Dad.
[TOSHIYA] Plus, it'll be
great publicity for the inn!
[YURI]
Dad.
[HIROKO] You'll autograph
a sign, won't you?
[YURI]
Until recently,
I thought I was fighting
all by myself.
But then, Victor came, and
I don't feel that way anymore.
Some things have changed.
Some are still the same.
But now everything feels so new.
I may never be able to regain
what I've lost, but that's okay.
Because for the first time
I can remember--I can clearly
see what's in front of me.
[music plays]
Okay, again.
From the beginning this time.
[gasps]
[YAKOV]
Huh...?
You're starting
to understand, Yuri.
Beautiful.
He was so reluctant
to begin with,
but he really is becoming
a prima ballerina.
[PLISETSKY]
I only have a short window
before my body begins to change.
I need to use every advantage
I have, while I still have it.
I will win.
[YURI] Figure skaters
are only competitive
for a short time.
[YURI]
This will probably be
my last competitive
skating season.
I don't how long
Victor will stay with me.
Or how long my
body will hold up.
So please, God,
while he is here,
help me make the most of
the time we have together.
One thing missing.
You haven't named the piece.
What are you going to call it?
Yeah. I'd say that's perfect.
[YURI]
Not long now. In September...
...my season with
Victor will finally begin.
[YURI]
My first competition in a while.
I'm nervous!
[VICTOR]
It's my coaching debut!
Yuri, what would you
like me to wear?
[YURI]
Uh, I dunno, clothes?
"Fifth Skate: Face Beet-Red!!
It's the First Competition!"
"The Chu-Shikoku-Kyushu
Regional Championship."
Stay tuned!