[theme music]
[crying]
[bell chiming]
-Ryuzaki.
Is something the matter?
What is it?
Hm?
What's wrong?
-Hm.
Interesting.
The corner of the page of this
notebook has been torn off.
Can you kill someone just by
writing their name on a piece?
-Can't say.
I've never tried
using it like that,
and I don't know
of anyone who has.
-Then let me ask you.
Do gods of death love apples?
-Not necessarily.
You see, our internal organs
have already degraded.
We've evolved to a point where
we do not require sustenance.
-Say, Light.
You're finally free to leave
headquarters on your own,
but it seems like
you never go out.
Even when Misa comes
to visit, you only
chat with her for a
few minutes outside.
You do realize you're free to
have a relationship with her
now?
-That can wait until we've
managed to solve this case.
I'm not in the mood for love
or anything else right now.
Anyway, are you
suggesting that I'll
be a nuisance for staying here?
-No.
LIGHT: Right now,
I'm in no position
to continue punishing criminals.
That's why I need you
to punish them for me.
Misa.
Let's create a new
world together.
-(SINGING) Careful what you
do, 'cause God is watching
your every move.
Hold my hand in the dark street.
For if you do, I know
that I'll be safe.
Even if I'm far
away and alone, I
can be sure that
you'll find me there.
This I know.
You draw me close for a while.
So quiet.
You tell me everything.
If I forget what you say,
then you'd come to me
and tell me again.
Yes, you'd tell me once again.
But what happens
when I know it all?
Then what should
I do after that?
What then?
-What's going on?
I heard criminals are
being killed again.
-There were 16 deaths
just yesterday.
All of them were broadcast
after Higuchi's death.
-Immediately after, huh?
-Do you think this could mean
that Higuchi wasn't necessarily
Kira after all?
-No.
It's safe to say that
Higuchi was the one killing
criminals until we
apprehended him.
-Then this means we're
dealing with yet another Kira.
-Aw, man!
Not again!
-Damn.
Damn you, Kira.
L (VOICEOVER): Another
Kira's appeared?
What's going on here?
REM (VOICEOVER): I
can't believe this.
It has to be Misa.
-These killings began as soon
as Misa was free, didn't they?
-Ryuzaki, are you still
going on about that?
She has nothing to do with this.
Think about it.
This started as soon
as Higuchi died.
-I suppose you're right.
Oh, well.
If there is another notebook
floating around out there
and someone is now using
it to kill criminals,
I'll just have to bring
that person to justice.
The Shinigami insisted
that it didn't know,
but if someone were
able to kill simply
by writing a name on a torn
piece of the notebook--
It's not impossible,
but there's that rule.
Whoever writes a
name in this notebook
has to write another
name within 13 days.
Otherwise, they die.
Light Yagami and Misa
Amane are both still alive.
13 days.
That's the only problem.
-Ryuzaki, I've
been thinking, even
if we do manage to catch the
person who's been writing names
in the notebook,
will we really be
able to legally convict and
punish them for mass homicide?
-What?
Of course we can convict them.
This guy's intentionally
writing names in the notebook,
knowing that these
people are going to die.
Even if we don't plan on
publicly acknowledging
the notebook, the least we
can do is execute the killer.
CHIEF YAGAMI: It's not a
very humane way to do things,
but the higher
ups would probably
want to take measures like that.
-If they admit to killing
with the notebook,
they'd receive the death
penalty, or life in prison,
at least.
That's the best that
they could hope for.
REM (VOICEOVER): What
are you thinking,
Light Yagami, making
Misa kill again?
She'll be caught, and
once that happens,
you'll also be-- So
that's what your plan is.
You're truly disgusting.
Light Yagami is certain
that I will do anything
to help Misa and save her life.
And at this point, the only
way for me to save Misa
is to write Ryuzaki's
real name in my notebook.
And if I kill Ryuzaki, it
would mean that I deliberately
lengthened Misa's life,
and I will die as well.
Light Yagami has
planned everything
so that it will work
out in his favor.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): What
are you gonna do, Rem?
You may be a Shinigami,
but you can't hide the fact
that you care for Misa.
There's no way you
would turn your back
on her now, after she's already
halved her lifespan twice.
Come on.
Think about Misa's happiness.
What are you doing, standing
out there by yourself?
(LOUDER) What are you doing
standing out there by yourself?
What are you doing, Ryuzaki?
-Oh, I'm not doing
anything in particular.
It's just, I hear the bell.
-The bell?
-Yes.
The sound of the bell is
being unusually loud today.
-Hm?
I don't hear anything.
-Really?
You can't hear it?
It's been ringing
nonstop all day.
I find it very distracting.
I wonder if it's a church?
Maybe a wedding, or perhaps a--
-What are you
getting at, Ryuzaki?
Come on, cut it out.
Let's get back inside.
-I'm sorry.
Nothing I say makes
any sense, anyway.
If I were you, I wouldn't
believe any of it.
-You know, you're totally right.
Honestly, most of the
things you say sound
like complete nonsense.
There'd be no end to my
troubles if I actually
took you seriously all the time.
I probably know that
better than anyone.
-Yes.
I would say that's
a fair assessment.
But I could say
the same about you.
-Hm?
What's that supposed to mean?
-Tell me, Light, from
the moment you were born,
has there ever
been a point where
you've actually told the truth?
-Where's this coming
from, Ryuzaki?
I do admit, I stretch
the truth here and there.
However, find me one
person in this world who's
never had to tell a lie.
It wouldn't be easy.
Human beings just aren't
made to be perfect like that.
Everybody lies
from time to time.
Even so, I've always
made a conscious effort
to be careful not to tell a
lie that could hurt others.
That's my answer.
-I had a feeling you'd
say something like that.
Let's go back inside.
We're both drenched.
LIGHT: Yeah.
-Well, that was certainly
an unpleasant outing.
-It's your own fault.
I mean, what did you expect?
L: You're right.
Sorry.
-What are you doing?
-I thought I might help you out.
You were busy wiping
yourself off, anyway.
-Look, it's fine.
You don't have to do that.
-I can give you a
massage, as well.
It's the least I can do
to atone for my sins.
I'm actually pretty
good at this.
-Fine.
Do what you want.
-All right.
-Hey.
-You'll get used to it.
-Here.
You're still soaked.
-I'm sorry.
It'll be lonely, won't it?
-Hm?
-You and I will be
parting ways soon.
[phone ringing]
-Yes?
I understand.
I'm on my way.
-Huh?
-Come on.
Let's go, Light.
It seems like it's
all worked out.
-Hm?
-Ryuzaki.
What's the meaning of all this?
You've somehow gotten
approval from another country
to use the notebook
for an execution?
-Watari.
Excellent work.
Thank you.
WATARI: Not at all.
-First things first.
Please make arrangements
to transport the notebook
immediately.
WATARI: Right.
-Ryuzaki, what are
you trying to do?
L: I'm going to try out
the notebook for real.
-We can't do that!
And there's no point
in testing it now
when we already know the
notebook's power is real.
-And besides, who's
gonna write the name?
If someone starts
writing in the notebook,
they'll have to obey
the 13 day rule,
and keep writing names forever.
L: It's already been worked out.
The person who will write in
the book is a criminal scheduled
to be executed is
just over 13 days.
If he's still alive 13 days
after writing the name,
he'll be pardoned
from execution.
-But still, to
sacrifice a life--
L: We're very close.
If we work this out, the
entire case will be solved.
[alarm]
-What is this?
A-- a blackout?
[gasping]
-Watari?
Watari!
-Data deletion?
What the hell's going on?
-I told Watari to make sure that
he should erase all information
in the event that something
were to happen to him.
-If something were to happen?
-Could it be--
-Where is the Shinigami?
-Good question.
I don't see it.
-It disappeared?
-What's going on?
-Everyone, the Shiniga--
[heartbeat]
-Ryuzaki!
What's wrong?
[bells ringing]
-Hey-- Ryuzaki.
Come on.
Snap out of it!
-What happened?
-What's going on?
[screaming]
-Calm down, Light.
-We're gonna die!
Watari, Ryuzaki.
It'll be us next!
Damn you!
Where are you, Shinigami?
Come out!
-Wait, Light.
-You know something
about this, don't you?
Come on out!
-We'd better go and look, too.
-Right.
-Mogi.
Take over for me.
-OK.
-There's something here!
-What the hell is this stuff?
-Sand?
-What does this mean?
-Whatever it might mean,
whatever happens next,
I swear I'll avenge
Ryuzaki's death.
We're going to solve
this case in honor
of him, and for Watari,
and all the other victims.
-Oh, Light.
-Let's do this.
For them.
-Yeah, but aren't we
all gonna get killed?
Isn't that what all
this really means?
-Matsuda.
If you're afraid of dying,
then leave the investigation.
We put our lives on the line
when we chose to be here.
-Yeah.
That's true.
But it-- it's weird
hearing you say that.
You sound like Ryuzaki.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I've gotten
rid of everything in my way.
I am the god of the New World.
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Ryuzaki, Watari, Rem.
I've gotten rid of
everything in my way.
I am the god of the New World.