[theme music]
INVESTIGATOR: Regarding
Naomi Misura's disappearance,
shouldn't we open an
investigation into this matter?
L: If we do, it should
be coordinated separately
from the Kira case.
Also, we'll have to use
police sketches instead
of actual photos.
-We're talking
about someone who's
been missing for
four months already.
Chances are, she's
probably dead.
-If you're right about
that, I find it odd
that we haven't
found her body yet.
If we did, it might provide
us with some much needed
physical evidence.
[knocking]
WATARI: Ryuzaki.
-Hmm?
-Something seems to be
happening on Sakura TV.
-In other words, all of
the reporters and staff
here are Kira's hostages.
Aside from that, we have
a professional obligation
to share this message with you.
I assure you that
this is not a hoax
and that Sakura TV is
not airing this tape
for the purposes
of sensationalism.
INVESTIGATOR: Kira's hostages?
What is this?
ANCHOR (TV): Four days
ago, our program director
here at Sakura TV
received four tapes.
After a thorough
examination, there
could be no doubt that
they are from Kira himself.
DIRECTOR (VOICEOVER):
Our audience
ratings should go up 60--
no, more like 70% after this.
ANCHOR (TV): The
first tape we received
contained a prediction regarding
the time of death of two
suspected criminals who'd
recently been arrested.
And as predicted, at the exact
time that Kira had specified,
both men died suddenly of
heart attacks yesterday.
L (VOICEOVER): If what
they're saying is true,
it's clearly something
that only Kira could do.
ANCHOR (TV): Kira
has instructed us
to air this second tape
today at exactly 5:59 PM.
And we do intend to
comply with his demands.
This tape should offer
proof of his powers
by predicting yet another death.
Beyond that, we understand
that it contains a message
to all the people of
the world from Kira.
--[gasp] Th--this has to be
another fake, don't you think?
-I doubt it.
I'm pretty sure even Sakura
TV wouldn't stoop that low.
ANCHOR (TV): And now, the video.
DISTORTED VOICE (TV):
[clearing throat] I am Kira.
If this video was being aired
on April 18 at exactly 5:59
PM as I requested, then the
time now is 5:59:47, 48, 49.
Please change the
channel to Taiyou TV.
The news anchor,
Mr. Kazuhi Kohibima,
will die of a heart attack
at exactly 6 o'clock.
[gasp]
-What?
-Change it.
[gasp]
INVESTIGATOR: It can't be.
-What happened?
-He's not moving.
-How could he?
-Change the channel back.
[beep]
And I need you to bring
us another TV, Watari.
No, make it two.
WATARI: Yes.
DISTORTED VOICE
(TV): --punishment.
I will present you
with another victim.
My next target is NHN
TV commentator Mr. Saeji
Komaizumi, who is scheduled
to appear in a live broadcast.
He too has dared to defy Kira.
INVESTIGATOR: Ryuzaki?
-Change it to channel 24.
[gasp]
-Someone help him!
L: Please change it back.
DISTORTED VOICE (TV): Now that
you've seen proof of my powers,
you should have no trouble
believing that I am Kira.
L (VOICEOVER): Kira
said that he was
going to send a message to
the people of the world.
[gasp] Stop this broadcast!
We can't let him finish!
-Get Sakura TV on the line!
-It's no good.
I'm trying, but none of
my contacts at the station
have their phones on.
-And nobody's picking
up at reception, either.
-Damn it!
And
-Ah, Ukita--
-I'll stop this broadcast
myself if that's what it takes.
DISTORTED VOICE (TV): People of
the world, please listen to me.
The last thing I want to
do is kill the innocent.
I hate evil and love justice.
I've always thought of
the police as allies,
not as enemies.
L (VOICEOVER): Damn you, Kira.
DISTORTED VOICE (TV):
I intend to create
a new world, a perfect world
that is free from evil.
If you agree to join
me in my mission,
I know we can make it happen.
And as long as no one
tries to catch me,
I promise that the
innocent will not die.
-Come on!
DISTORTED VOICE (TV): Even
if you don't agree with me,
all I ask is that
you not publicize
your views in the media.
If you can do that,
you will be spared.
All you have to do
now is be patient.
I will create a better
world that we can all enjoy.
Say goodbye to the
world as you know it.
Soon, we'll have a new world
ruled by benevolence, inhabited
with kind-hearted,
honest people.
Try to imagine it, a world
where the police and I--
-Hmm?
Sachiko.
-Darling, this can't be
good for your health.
Please, you have to rest.
-Sachiko, like it
or not, I am still
in charge of the
Kira task force.
[sigh]
-Damn, it's locked!
This is the police!
Open up!
Ah, you-- you idiots!
[groaning, hearteat]
-Hello?
REPORTER (TV): We interrupt
this program to bring you live--
-Damn, I'm still
not getting through.
REPORTER (TV):
--Sakura TV studios.
-[gasp] Aizawa, look!
-Huh?
[gasp]
REPORTER (TV): As
you can see, someone
has collapsed just
outside the door.
Again, we're coming to you live
from the Sakura TV building.
AIZAWA: Ukita-- damn
it, Kira did this.
-[grumble] Mr. Aizawa.
Where are you going?
-Where do you think?
I've got to go there.
-You can't.
Please, think about
this rationally.
-(ANGRILY) What, you want me
to just sit here and watch TV?
-If this truly is
the work of Kira,
you'll just meet the same
fate if you go there.
-You told us that Kira
couldn't kill without a name.
So how could this happen?
The aliases and fake
police IDs are worthless.
What are we going to do, L?
You don't think Kira has all
our names already, do you?
-That's a definite possibility.
However, if that's
the case, you'd
think it would be easier for
him to kill off the entire task
force before making a move.
Initially, I deduced that Kira
needed both a name and a face
to kill.
But from what we've
just seen, I'd
say it's not entirely
impossible that Kira
can kill with only a face.
All I know for sure is that Kira
is either in that TV station,
or he's somewhere close
by, in a place where
he can watch everyone
who enters the building.
Perhaps he's in an--
-If Kira is in the area,
then isn't that why
we should get down there?
L: For all we know, he could
have just placed surveillance
cameras in the area.
If we rush down there
unprepared, all of us
will be killed.
-Wasn't it you who said we'd
have to risk our lives to catch
Kira?
-I meant what I said, but
risking my life to catch Kira
and doing something that I
know will cost me my life
are two entirely
different things.
-Oh yeah?
-Please control yourself.
We've lost Ukita.
I understand you
want to go there,
but if something was to
happen to you as well--
-I now await a response
from the police.
They must decide
whether or not they'll
help me create a better
world for all of us.
Please announce your decision
on the 6 o'clock news
in four days.
I've prepared two
videos, one to be
aired if the answer is yes and
another if the answer is no.
[sigh]
[gasp]
[growl]
-Huh?
[scream]
What the hell's going on?
Hey, step out of the vehicle!
Huh?
-The Kira video.
Show me which studio they're
broadcasting it from.
REPORTER (TV): A
vehicle has just
driven through the front
doors of the station.
-Well, that's one way
to get into the building
without being seen by Kira.
INVESTIGATOR: But who would--
-This is the police.
Stop this broadcast immediately.
-Who are you?
-Hand those tapes over to me.
Do you understand?
-Hold on, officer.
It's not that simple.
My hands are tied here.
If we stop this broadcast,
he'll kill all of us.
-Shut up.
You're going to be
killed right here and now
if you don't give
those tapes to me.
-What?
Come on, what the hell do
you think you're doing?
This is crazy.
-This is happening because you
chose to make Kira a celebrity.
You're getting exactly
what you deserve.
I want every single
copy you have,
and don't make me ask you again.
-I-I got it.
I'll give them to you.
No problem.
Just please, stop
waving that gun around.
You're acting like a madman.
REPORTER (TV): We're
still outside Sakura TV.
As you can see, a police
car has just arrived.
-So we're not alone.
There are still other
officers out there
who are willing to
stand up to Kira.
L: Mr. Aizawa.
-Huh?
-You know Deputy Director
Kitamura's cell phone number,
right?
[phone ringing]
-Aizawa, I told you not
to call me on this phone.
L (ON PHONE): This is L.
[gasp]
L (ON PHONE): There's something
I need you to do for me.
There may be police officers
who will see this broadcast
and feel moved to take action
in the name of justice.
If you don't take control
of this situation quickly,
there will be a disaster.
-But technically,
we're not supposed
to be involved in this case.
Huh?
REPORTER (TV): [gasp] Two
police officers have just
collapsed on the sidewalk.
I-- I think we may be in danger.
We're moving away
from the scene.
-I understand, L. I
see your point now.
Tell me what I should do.
[phone ringing]
-Detective
Superintendent Yagami.
L: Call him back immediately
and give me the phone.
-I need to speak with Ryuzaki.
-Yes, it's me.
Mr. Yagami.
So you're the one
driving the police van.
-That's right.
I couldn't just sit and watch.
I've confiscated
all of the tapes.
I'm bringing them to you.
But what about your condition?
Are you all right?
-I'm feeling just fine.
To be honest with
you, I don't think
I've ever felt more alive.
So what do you think
I should do now?
I'd say going out the front
will be too dangerous,
but I could always use
the police van again.
-Please hold the
line for a second.
Deputy Director Kitamura,
it was Chief Yagami
who just drove
into the building.
Are your preparations complete?
-It's done, as you requested.
-Mr. Yagami, listen carefully.
In exactly five
minutes, I want you
to come out the front entrance.
-You want me to exit
through the front entrance?
[gasp]
POLICE OFFICER (ON BULLHORN):
Make sure there are no gaps.
Do not reveal your faces.
We know that Kira is
not in the building.
He is outside.
-Thank you.
I'll drive myself.
IDE: I understand.
POLICE OFFICER (ON
BULLHORN): Listen up.
There is a very good
chance that Kira is still
in the vicinity of the station.
As you move out,
proceed with caution.
You are not to
remove your helmets.
KOKI TANAKABARA (TV):
There you have it.
The police refuse to
cooperate with Kira.
Instead, they are
preparing to fight.
And, as much as I fear for
my own life in saying so,
this is right.
And it must be done.
Kira has become a threat
to our very constitution.
And as citizens,
we must fight back.
I am NHN's Golden news
anchor, Koki Tanakabara.
-Mm?
Chief Yagami!
AIZAWA: Welcome back, Chief.
-Mm.
Ryuzaki, I apologize for taking
matters into my own hands.
I have to admit, I got a
little bit carried away.
-No.
-Here, these are all of
the tapes in an envelope.
Everything Kira sent to
the station is in here.
L: I can't thank you enough.
-Ah, I think I'd better
rest for a minute.
[groan]
L (VOICEOVER): Mr. Yagami,
this won't go to waste.
The postmark is from Osaka, but
Kira can control his victims
before they die, so he could
have delivered it from Osaka
without going there himself.
Mr. Aizawa, can you please
take this to the crime lab
right away?
-I still have a couple
of friends down there.
I'll make sure they go
over every inch of this.
-That's good.
Please do so.
While you're doing
that, I'm going
to watch these tapes to see
if they can tell us anything.
CHIEF YAGAMI: Well, what
do you make of these?
-They were definitely
interesting.
If the police had said yes and
agreed to cooperate with Kira,
tape number three was
supposed to be aired.
Tape four if the answer was no.
Tape three covers the
terms of cooperation.
Put simply, he's
requesting that we
broadcast the names
of more criminals.
He seems particularly interested
in those who have assaulted
others or those who have
somehow hurt or taken
advantage of the
weak and defenseless.
Of course, Kira would play the
role of judge in all of this.
Furthermore, as
proof that the police
are willing to cooperate, he
wants police officials and L
to appear on TV, to make a
public announcement that we
plan to cooperate with him.
-Huh?
-He needs us to
reveal our faces.
That way, he can kill us if the
police do anything suspicious.
In other words, he'll hold
our lives as insurance.
-I see.
So what about the content
of the fourth video
if we were to answer no?
-The wording was different,
but he more or less
says the same thing.
Mr. Yagami, it should go without
saying that the answer is no.
Please have someone take tape
numer four over to Sakura TV
and authorize them
to broadcast it.
DISTORTED VOICE
(TV): I can only say
it's a shame that
your answer is no.
It's clear that the
police wish to oppose me.
This will not go unpunished.
So I'll start by taking the life
of either the director-general
of the NPA or the detective
known as L, who is currently
leading the
investigation against me.
The director-general or L?
Who will pay the
price for your refusal
to cooperate in the creation
of a peaceful world?
You have four days to decide.
[laughing]
-Hmm.
It looks like I've even
got God on my side now.
Well, I suppose it's
actually a god of death.
-Heh, seems like it.
-It would appear that
another Shinigami
has come to the human world.
And somehow, that
Shinigami's Death Note
has fallen into the hands of
someone who agrees with Kira.
And this person most likely
has the Shinigami eyes,
which makes him very deadly.
His power to kill
surpasses even mine.
One thing is for certain.
If I leave things,
I'm pretty sure that L
will be finished off
within the next four days.
However, I can't
forgive this impostor
for the way he's
tarnishing Kira's
image with these
senseless killings.
Not to mention, if he
slips up and gets caught,
the Death Note
could be discovered.
And that, I cannot allow.
I can't afford to leave
him alone for much longer.
[laughing]
Therefore, what needs
to happen very soon
is for me to join
the task force.
It'll allow me to keep track
of L and this fake Kira.
-Ryuzaki, I'm afraid
it's as you thought.
Several of our member
countries have weighed in,
and it seems they are
in favor of having
the real L appear on TV.
-I think that's the most
appropriate choice, given
the options.
Well, we still have three
days before it happens.
Maybe we can find
some countermeasure.
After all this, it would
really annoy me-- [slurp]
--mm-- if I'm killed
by the first person
to jump on the Kira bandwagon.
[gasp]
-Ryuzaki, what do
you mean by that?
-That there's a
strong possibility
that this Kira's a fake.
No, we should think of
him more as a second Kira.
-A second Kira?
-I-- I don't understand.
Why do you think
there's a copycat?
How did you come
to that conclusion?
L: I looked at the victims
he used for his predictions
on tape number one.
Their purpose was to
prove to Sakura TV staff
that he is Kira.
Both their names
were only reported
in tabloids and
daytime talk shows,
so they weren't exactly
hardened criminals.
The real Kira has no
need to prove himself
using such
insignificant criminals.
But from the
perspective Kira, he'd
want to make absolutely
certain that he didn't predict
the death of a
criminal who could
be killed by the
real Kira first.
-Hmm.
Ryuzaki, if you had to
put a number on it, what's
the probability
of a second Kira?
-This time, I'd say
it's more than 70%.
-[gasp]
-I really don't like
the way he operates.
It's not like Kira.
-Not like him?
L: In the past, he
has traditionally
avoided killing innocent people,
with the exception of those
who were trying to catch him.
Anyway, if we can
capture one Kira,
I think that will provide
us with a lot of insight
into how we can
find the other one.
Mr. Yagami, I'd
like your permission
to ask your son to cooperate
with us on this investigation.
-Huh?
-If you want my son to
join the task force,
does this mean you no
longer suspect him?
-Well, I can't say that he's
been completely cleared,
but his deductive abilities
would be invaluable to us
right now.
CHIEF YAGAMI (VOICEOVER)
So that's what it means.
If my son wants to
cooperate with you,
then I have no
reason to prevent it.
-I appreciate that.
However, please don't
tell him that we
think this latest
Kira might be a fake.
I don't want him
to know that yet.
We want to make it appear
to him that we're still
chasing the same Kira.
-Hmm.
REM: Misa, I gave that
Death Note to you.
So why not use it for yourself?
-I am using it for
myself because I
believe in what Kira is doing.
I want to know what
kind of person Kira is.
I want to meet him
and talk to him.
That's the only reason I sent
all those videos to that TV
station.
I had to find some way
to make Kira notice me.
And I'd say that probably
got his attention.
Don't you think?
[giggle]
-It's a dangerous
game you're playing.
There's a chance
you could be killed.
Do you understand?
-It's all right.
I'm sure that Kira is kind
to those with pure hearts.
And if it came down to
that, I'm still stronger
than he is because
I have the eyes.
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I need to figure out
what this other
Kira is all about
before someone else on the
task force beats me to it.
I wonder, what kind of
person are you, impostor?