[theme music]
-Near, if you don't
mind me asking,
what do you make of all this?
I'm interested to hear what
your thoughts are on this case.
-The current Kira is
foolish and overconfident.
Not to mention
unusually cooperative
with the task force.
So much so that I suspect he's
working hand in hand with them.
-You think so?
-That would make the
second L and Kira one
in the same person.
-What?
That can't be.
Are-- Are you serious?
-Yes, I am.
Having said that, I'll admit
that I'm only 7% certain.
Don't worry, Commander Rester.
Making assumptions is
part of any investigation.
If we're wrong, all
it'll cost is an apology.
WOMAN: There have been
less crimes lately
in Japan, and around the world.
It's because of Kira.
My daddy told mee that,
if you do something bad,
your name will be
written on the internet--
-Your name, please?
WOMAN: --and Kira will kill you.
-Come on.
I don't have all day.
How am I supposed to file
this report without your name?
-Will you give me a break?
Please, not my name!
Leave me alone or I'll put
your names on the internet.
MAN: I will proclaim
this right here and now,
to all the people of the Earth.
Kira is true justice!
Good evening.
It is my honor to be appointed
by Kira as his spokesman.
This is not a hoax.
It's the absolute truth.
I realize that there
will be many people who
might try to have me killed now.
But, I'm prepared
to risk by life--
-Kira's Kingdom, huh?
What a horrible title.
-This is insanity.
- --can hear Kira's voice.
Trying to capture Kira
is an unforgivable crime.
If you happen to know--
-If anybody deserves to be
killed by Kira, it's this guy.
MAN: --a criminal,
or a regular citizen.
-Switch it back to
the press conference.
The president's about to start.
I wonder what it's about.
All they said was
that it was going
to be some sort of
international announcement.
-You don't do anything
but watch TV, do you?
-Wha--
-Good morning.
I'm gonna try to
keep this brief.
-No way.
-The United States will
no longer oppose Kira.
-Those cowards!
I've done it.
I've even been brought
America to its knees.
-What the hell is
he talking about?
-Have they been
threatened or something?
-Are you saying that
Kira is justice?
-Justice?
No, no, I never said that.
But because if Kira, war and
conflict have ceased to exist.
Criminal organizations
are in a state of ruin,
not only in the United States,
but in all free nations.
Anyone who defies Kira
head on will be killed.
That is a fact.
We are not acknowledging
Kira as a symbol of justice.
We are simply saying
that, as a country,
we will not take any
actions against him.
MAN: How is that any different?
-You're saying that
you accept Kira?
Explain yourself!
-You call yourself a
representative of our country?
-I can't believe it.
This is America.
How can their government
do something so cowardly
like this?
-Uh.
Do you guys mind if I
ask a serious question?
-Oh, boy.
What is it this time?
-Are you telling us
you're not always serious?
-Do you guys ever
think that maybe Kira
isn't completely evil?
-What?
-What kind of question
is that, Matsuda?
-I've been thinking
about it, and part of me
just doesn't believe that he is.
-So now you think
Kira is justice too?
-I don't really know.
But I think that Kira's trying
to fight evil and change
the world in his
own way and, well,
the world's become a
good place for people
who live honest
lives, so maybe--
-You're wrong, Matsuda!
People are only afraid of
losing their own lives.
How can you think
that's real peace?
-I understand that.
Believe me, I know
that as well as you.
It's just that I can also
understand the other side.
I can see why all those
people call Kira a savior.
I'm not like you.
When it comes down
to it, I've always
been a really weak person.
But I'm also a detective.
I can't accept Kira.
I know it's my
duty to catch him.
No, I want to catch him.
It's just that I can't
completely hate him either.
I guess I must be crazy
or something, huh?
-No, you're not crazy.
You're normal.
-You too, Light?
What are you talking about?
-I'm sure that, on some
level, Kira probably
knows that what
he's doing is evil,
but he'll try to change the
world, even as a martyr,
at the cost of his soul.
That's his brand of justice.
I bet that's what's going
through Kira's mind.
Anyway, we shouldn't
be arguing about it.
Good or evil, it's not our call.
All we have to think
about is catching him.
If Kira gets caught,
then that makes him evil.
But if he wins and
rules the world,
then I guess he's justice.
But from now on, the world will
start leaning in favor of Kira.
It's only a matter of time.
Kira will be justice.
-What's going to
happen to us now?
-It looks like we've
been disbanded,
thanks to that chicken
of a president.
No.
He's not even a chicken.
He's less than a maggot.
You've got to be kidding.
There's no way accepting Kira
will lead to anything good.
-Huh?
Huh?
So you're alive.
-Near.
-Hm?
-What should we do?
-Let him in.
Mello, welcome.
-Drop your weapon!
-Everyone, please
put away your guns.
Having a shoot out here
would achieve nothing.
Sir, with all due respect.
Mello's the one who
killed our partners.
-Please don't make
me say it again.
Remember that our primary
objective is still
to catch Kira.
Killing Mello right
now will do nothing
to benefit our investigation.
-All right.
-It seems like things
have been going
just as you planned, Near.
NEAR: Yes.
I take it you've already
heard all about the second L
from Lidner by now.
I've pretty much
figured out who Kira is,
and it's mostly thanks to
everything you've done.
-Shut up, Near!
I'm not just a tool
for you to use in order
to solve your puzzles, you know.
-Mello.
If you really want to shoot
me, then go ahead and do it.
-Stop.
If you shoot him,
then the rest of us
will have no choice
but to shoot you too.
What will it solve
if both of you die?
That's just what Kira wants.
-You have a good point.
Anyway, I'm only
here for one thing.
I came to take back that
photograph you have.
-Of course.
I got it from the orphanage.
There was only one and
no copies have been made.
I've already gone
ahead and dealt
with everyone who knows
your face, both inside
and outside Wammy's house.
they'll keep quiet.
I can't say 100% for certain,
but it shouldn't be possible
for you to be killed
by the notebook.
Is that the only business
you had with me, Mello?
-Near.
Let's get one thing straight.
I have no intention of working
together with you on this.
-Yes, I know.
-At the same time, I can't
just take my photo and leave.
That wouldn't be right.
So I'll settle my debt.
The killer notebook.
It belongs to a Shinigami.
Whoever touches it is able
to see a god of death.
-That's crazy.
-Who the hell would believe
in something like that?
NEAR: I would.
I believe him completely.
What good would it do for
him to tell an outrageous lie
like that?
Even if he had
something to gain,
he could at least come up
with a more believable story.
Therefore, these gods
of death must exist.
-The notebook I
obtained had previously
belonged to another Shinigami,
perhaps even Kira himself.
Also, some of the rules written
inside are actually fake.
That's all I can
tell you for now.
Near.
-Mello?
-Which of us is going to
reach Kira first, I wonder?
-The race is on.
-We're both headed towards
the same destination.
I'll be waiting for you.
-Right.
Fake rules.
There's no doubt
that the notebook can
cause heart attacks and control
its victims to a degree.
As for burning it
or tearing it up,
the notebook still
exists, and there's
no way to confirm the
rule one way or the other.
That means-- the
false rule must be
the one that states
a person will
die if he doesn't write
a name within 13 days.
Giovanni.
Please set up a connection to L.
-Yes, sir.
-It's Near.
Yes?
-NEAR: L, I thought you should
know that we caught Mello.
-Huh?
-But he escaped soon afterwards.
We were able to interrogate
him for a while.
-He didn't really
escape, did he?
You let him get away.
Am I right?
-No.
We tried to restrain him,
but he was too quick.
Anyway, Mello
mentioned that there
was some sort of Shinigami
attached to the notebook.
Have you been able to
confirm the existence of such
a creature?
-Yes.
I can tell you for a fact
that Shinigami do exist.
I didn't share that information
with you at the beginning
because I was certain you
would never believe me.
NEAR: I would like to ask the
Shinigami a few questions.
-Forget it.
I'm not up for that.
-The thing that's bothering
me the most about this
is the issue of those rules
written in the notebook.
I have reason to believe
that one of them is fake.
-Huh?
-A fake rule?
NEAR: Yes.
L, I'd be interested to
hear your thoughts on this.
Out of all the rules, which
do you think is the fake?
I'd like to know.
-By process of elimination,
the obvious choice
would be the one stating
that the owner of a notebook
will die if they don't write a
new name in it every 13 days.
I don't believe that.
NEAR: I thought
you might say so.
I've reached the
same conclusion.
-Shinigami, you know the
rules of the notebook rule.
Tell us, are any of them false?
-No.
They are all real.
-I see.
You have a Shinigami
there with you?
-Yes.
-Is that so?
I think I'm beginning
to get the picture.
In other words, Kira
is there in the room,
and he's making the
Shinigami lie on his behalf.
RYUK (VOICEOVER):
Whoa, this guy's good.
He nailed it.
-I don't get what he means.
So what if the Shinigami is
lying, and the rule's fake?
It doesn't really change
anything, does it?
-Yes, it does.
It means that
Light's incarceration
would be meaningless.
The rule says you die if you
don't continue writing names.
But if that's false, being
alive after more than 13 days
in confinement wouldn't
really prove anything.
-But even if that's true,
it doesn't mean he's guilty.
Besides, there's no way
that Light can be Kira.
Before he passed away,
the deputy director
himself was able to confirm
that he didn't have a notebook.
NEAR: If there's a
problem, I suggest
we verify the rule this way.
I will volunteer to write
down Mello's real name
in the notebook.
Of course, that means he'll die.
If I also die 13 days later,
well, then I guess Kira wins.
Either way, it's a gamble
I'm quite willing to make.
-What?
So this is just a game to him?
-Testing and confirming
the 13 day rule
can only benefit the
Kira investigation.
And other than my
possible death,
there would be no drawbacks.
I'm willing to put
my life on the line
if it will help
us solve the case.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): If I answer
him based on my feelings alone,
it will only make me
look worse to everyone.
Could you please
wait for a moment?
We need to discuss
your suggestion.
OK.
What are your thoughts?
We can say that we
must respect human life
and deny this request,
but I can't suggest that.
I'm the one under suspicion.
-It's a tough call.
Mello killed the
deputy director.
If Near is willing,
I wouldn't stop him.
-I'm against the idea, myself.
I don't believe that
Kira is hiding among us.
We can't use the notebook,
no matter what happens.
-We should respect the deputy
director's wishes to the end.
-I feel the same.
I'm opposed to the test.
-Hm.
Near, we've talked
it over, and we
can't allow you to use
the notebook like that.
-I had a feeling
you might say so.
No matter.
Just one last
question before I go.
To the members of the
Japanese task force,
was there ever a point in
the investigation where
the second L was
suspected to be Kira,
even if the suspicions
were later dropped?
If you've been listening
to our conversation so far
and have any intention of
helping my investigation
in taking down Kira,
then call the number
I'm about to give you.
Day or not, I will answer.
The choice is up to you.
(VOICEOVER) There's no way
that Light could be Kira.
No, it's more like I don't
want to believe he's Kira.
But if the 13 day rule
is fake, then we really
can't say for sure
that he's innocent.
This could change everything.
[laughter]
-(VOICEOVER) Near.
I have to kill him.
[phone ringing]
-Yes?
Hello?
MODIFIED VOICE: This is Kira.
-Is this a joke?
MODIFIED VOICE:
If you want proof,
I can read out a list
of people that I'm
going to punish tomorrow.
That way you can check it
and make your final decision
afterwards.
Mr. President, I am
very grateful that you
and your country have
sympathized with me,
but I'm afraid even
that much isn't enough.
The SPK is still
trying to catch me,
despite your recent
announcement.
I want you to stop them
immediately, and formally
disband them.
At the same time, I want you
to use the American police,
the CIA, the FBI, and all other
law enforcement organizations
at your disposal to find out
where the SPK members are
currently hiding.
As soon as you've found
their base of operations,
I want you to forward that
information to a third party.
I will give you this
contact shortly.
Mr. President, whether you
live a long life or not
is up to you.
Don't forget that.
-I understand.
MAN: Mr. Demegawa,
please wait a moment.
-Why are you going to New York?
-We are going to crush
an organization that
dares to defy Kira.
it will be on live TV.
This is a direct
order from Kira,
and it came through the
President of the United States
himself.
-Huh?
-I don't know what's going
to happen when we get there.
Hell, I don't even know
what I'm saying anymore,
and I don't really care.
Sakura TV's ratings are
gonna rocket to 100-- no,
120% for this special.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Come on, everyone!
The new age of Kira
is about to arrive!
-(VOICEOVER) The previous
L was suspicious of Light.
But if Light is Kira, and
I just come out and say
we should investigate again,
then I'll probably end up dead,
just like L. That
won't solve anything.
The 13 day rule, huh?
IDE: Aizawa.
-Huh?
-We have a long history.
I can tell exactly what
you're thinking about,
and what's bothering you.
Between you and me,
you should go ahead
and do what you think is right.
I didn't trust L to begin with.
I never did, to be honest.
I didn't sign up to
join the Kira task
force because Light
was running it.
I joined because I
wanted to work with you.
-Ide.
All right.
I'll see if I can contact Near
without letting Light know.
IDE: OK.
I'll make sure that no one
knows what you're doing.
You can count on me.
-(VOICEOVER) Light, I really
want to believe that you're not
Kira.
-This is really bad.
Turn on the TV.
It's Demegawa!
-Huh?
-This is Demegawa live.
My comrades and I have
finally pinpointed the hideout
of the evil organization
bent on trying
to catch our beloved god Kira.
We now have the building
completely surrounded!
MAN: Come on out!
Break down the door!
DEMEGAWA: Right now
our enemies appear
to be hiding within
the building,
but they won't be able
to hide from us for long.
Behold the power of the people!
The power of justice!
MISA (VOICEOVER): As
soon as Near escapes, I'm
gonna write his name
in the notebook.
Don't worry, Light.
I won't let you down.
-At this rate, we'll be dragged
outside unless we stop them
somehow.
NEAR (VOICEOVER): L.
-What's going on, Near?
Could it be that this is
some sort of plot by Mello
to finish off the SPK?
No.
Surely it couldn't be that
the SPK's security was so lax
that even a normal citizen could
find out where it was located.
NEAR (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
He's lying through his teeth.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I win, Near.
[theme music]
LIGHT: I can definitely
use this man.
He worships Kira from
the bottom of his heart.
He understands
that he was chosen
the moment he took
possession of the notebook.
There was no mistake
in my selection.