[theme music]
-I hereby relinquish
ownership of this Death Note.
-Take care of her.
You gave your word.
-Huh?
[whimpers] Mr. Stalker?
Hello, Mister?
Where are you right now?
Do-- do you think we
could stop this game?
-Huh?
MAN: Stalker?
Where'd she get that?
What's with the new
attitude all of a sudden?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Just as I thought.
As long as I still
have Ryuk's notebook,
even though I gave up Rem's, all
awareness I have of Rem still
remains.
Rem, the only reason I have
to go through all this trouble
is because you brought another
Death Note to the human world.
-Is this really what
you want, Light?
-Yeah.
-OK.
I never thought the
Death Note I gave
you would end up
buried and abandoned.
Listen, Ryuk.
For the time being,
I'm just hiding it.
But it stays mine,
until the next time
you hear me say the following
words-- get rid of it.
When I say that,
regardless of the context,
assume that I want to relinquish
ownership of this Death Note.
-Got it.
-Mr. Stalker?
This is illegal.
You have to stop.
OK?
Come on, please?
-She's been acting
like this ever
since she regained
consciousness.
-Seriously.
Does she think she can get out
of this just by playing dumb?
-OK.
How about this?
You could at least
take off my blindfold.
Don't you think?
It'll be nice to see
what you look like.
-Matsuda, call Mogi for me.
-Huh?
Just a second.
Here.
-Mr. Mogi, when you apprehended
Misa Amane, you made it clear
that she was a
suspect, am I correct?
-Yes, like you told me.
First, I blindfolded her
and covered her mouth.
I told her that we knew
she was the second Kira.
I made sure that she heard me.
She didn't struggle when I put
the blindfold and handcuffs
on her.
It was like she'd accepted it.
-What if I gave you an
autograph, or shook your hang?
I know.
I can give you a kiss on
the cheek of you want.
Oh, come on.
I won't run away.
I promise.
L (VOICEOVER): We'd already
made so much progress with her,
I actually thought she'd crack.
Why is she suddenly
talking about a stalker?
DISTORTED VOICE (ON
SPEAKER): Misa Amane.
-Huh?
What's that, Mr. Stalker?
Are you planning to release me?
DISTORTED VOICE (ON SPEAKER):
Before you passed out,
you barely spoke.
And you even asked
me to kill you.
And now you're
claiming ignorance?
-Hm?
I don't understand.
I mean, you're the one who
knocked me out and then brought
me here, remember?
Wait.
I get it.
This is some kind of Misa Amane
interrogation fantasy, right?
-Huh?
-Do you know why I'm
detaining you here?
You must have some idea.
MISA (ON SPEAKER):
What do you mean?
Because I'm a
celebrity, obviously.
But you're definitely
the first stalker
who's ever gone this far.
And you're starting to scare me.
-Hey, Amane!
No one's buying
this, so cut it out.
-Oh, this is scary.
What's going on?
I can't stand it anymore!
Please let me go!
You have to let me go!
I-- I need to go
to the bathroom.
I have to go to the
bathroom again, OK?
DISTORTED VOICE (ON
SPEAKER): It's only
been four minutes since you
last went to the bathroom.
I'm afraid you'll
have to hold it.
-You have to.
It's the only time you'll
untie me and let me move.
Plus, you'd be able to watch.
Isn't that what you want?
Isn't it?
You pervert!
-I'm a pervert?
Amane, let's get back
to the conversation
we were having before
you lost consciousness.
First of all, do you
know who Light Yagami is.
And if so, why did
you approach him?
-Huh?
What do you mean?
How can I not know
my own boyfriend?
L (VOICEOVER): She was so
tight-lipped about it earlier.
Now she's openly admitting
he's her boyfriend?
-Where is this coming from?
[phone ringing]
-Good timing.
It's Light.
-Please turn the
video and audio off.
WATARI (ON SPEAKER): Yes.
L: Yes?
Yes, I understand.
We'll be expecting
you in room K-2801.
-Are you saying my
son's coming here?
-Ryuzaki, like I said over
the phone, I could be Kira.
-[gasp] No, Light.
What are you talking about?
Why would you even say
something like that?
Why?
L (VOICEOVER):
There's no real proof
that Light Yagami
is Kira, so why
come here that
you could be Kira?
It's an act.
There's no "could be" about it.
You are Kira.
What do you hope to
accomplish by this?
-Look, Dad.
If Ryuzaki is L,
then it's safe to say
that he is the world's
best detective.
And right now, he seems
pretty sure that I'm Kira.
We know L's never
been wrong before.
-What-- what are
you saying, Light?
Stop this.
LIGHT: What about that
FBI agent, Ray Penber?
It was me he was investigating
immediately before he died.
And I was in Oyama on May 22.
Also, I'm the first
person in the Kanto region
that Misa, the alleged
second Kira, approached.
It's all been me.
If I were in L's
place, even I would
have come to the
same conclusion.
You see, subconsciously,
I might be Kira.
If that were the case, I could
be him and not even know it.
-No, Light.
L (VOICEOVER): I see.
So you're not
conscious of it, huh?
-I-- I'm not sure
of anything anymore.
I'd never kill someone,
but unconsciously,
who knows what I'm capable of?
Another me could be
killing people as I sleep.
-I'm afraid that's not possible.
-Huh?
Not possible?
What do you mean?
-Well, I never mentioned this
to you, but at one point,
I had hidden surveillance
cameras installed
in your room for five days.
-Cameras?
-Yes.
Every single night,
you slept normally.
Criminals whose
names were broadcast
were still dying,
even though you
would have had no way
of knowing about them.
But this didn't prove
your innocence to me.
All it proved was
that if you were Kira,
no amount of camera surveillance
would reveal that fact.
-Wouldn't reveal that fact, huh?
I don't know.
It could be true.
I have to admit, I
found myself thinking
that some criminals
deserve to die.
If I can think
like Kira, then how
can I be sure that
I'm not actually him?
-Hold on, Light.
I feel exactly the same way.
I found myself thinking
before that some people would
be better off dead.
But still, that
doesn't mean we're
going to go out and kill people.
Isn't that right?
Besides, criminals
were still being
killed, even while you
had no knowledge of them.
I mean, the surveillance
cameras proved it, didn't they?
-Well, no.
Because we were short
of investigators then,
we only watched him
while he was at home.
Truth is, we weren't
able to watch
him every hour of the day.
It's possible he could
have found some way
to kill those criminals
well he wasn't at home.
L (VOICEOVER): This
was premeditated.
It's no accident he
chose to do this now.
Well, what if we
incarcerate you for a while,
imprison you like we did Amane?
If criminals whose names
are made public keep dying,
then it would lead us to think
that you're innocent, right?
Is that how you imagined it?
L: Honestly, I don't like the
way that this is going at all,
but what choice do I have?
Let's do it.
I need you to fully
restrain Light Yagami
and place him in
solitary confinement.
-What?
You can't!
-You want us to confine him?
Seriously?
L: If we're going
to do this, then it
has to happen immediately.
From this point on,
you can't be allowed
to go anywhere where
I can't see you.
-This is crazy.
There's no way my
son could be Kira.
My son's not capable of--
-It's OK, Dad.
-Stop this, Light.
Listen, something has
to be done about this.
As long as I'm
having these doubts,
I can't work with
you to catch Kira.
But Ryuzaki, promise me this.
Until you can say with absolute
certainty that I'm not Kira,
you cannot set me free, no
matter what I might say or what
condition I might be in.
-You have my word.
Mr. Yagami, can you
come up with some sort
of excuse for Light's absence,
something to tell your family?
And please do it now.
-But this is all so sudden.
What should I say?
And then I see no reason
why he should be in prison.
-Let it go, Dad.
-Huh?
-If I don't do this, I won't
be able to live with myself.
--[gasp] But son, do
you really mean that?
-Yeah.
I believe that by giving
up my very freedom,
I'll defeat this fear
that Kira lurks within me.
L: Aizawa, please take him away.
-Right.
-Hm.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Next,
I just have to get rid
of the notebook.
-So, I guess apples are
out of the question?
-Ryuzaki, I'd like to
request that you take me
off this investigation.
-Chief, no!
-But why?
-I thought about
it, and the fact
is that we're holding my son,
Light, as a prime suspect.
Given that, it's not
appropriate for me to be here.
When we spoke earlier, my
feelings got in the way.
It's impossible for me to be
objective in this situation.
-I agree with you.
We can't let personal
feelings get in the way.
-And in truth, if--
if the task force
concludes that my
son is Kira, I don't
know what I'd be capable of.
L: Yes, I'll agree
with you there.
To be honest, I wondered
what you might do.
I believe you'd kill your
son and then yourself.
I'd also agree that
it's best that we
don't have you
working here for now.
-Ryuzaki, I will ask that
you confine me as well.
[gasping]
-At the moment, I'm calm.
But to be honest, I'm not
sure how much more of this I
can take.
I thought you might say that.
So I spoke with Watari.
He's made arrangements.
[gasping]
-Mm, but, your confinement
will be different.
You will keep your
cell phone turned on
and maintain regular contact
with family and friends.
You won't tell Light about this.
If he does call
you at some point,
he must be made to believe that
you're still at headquarters.
While you're in
confinement, we'll
be giving you continuous
updates on the investigation.
So you'll know what's happening.
So how does that sound to you?
-I'm grateful.
Thank you.
MISA (ON SPEAKER): Hey, Mister,
I really want to take a bath.
I'm pretty sure you already
know where I live, don't you?
Could you bring me
some clean clothes.
-I didn't think this could
get any more bizarre.
-I feel so sorry for
the chief right now.
-Ryuzaki talk to me.
What's happening?
Have any new criminals
been identified,
anyone that Kira would
be likely to target?
If so, has he
killed any of them?
-In fact, quite a
few criminals' names
have been broadcast recently.
But since you've
been detained, we
haven't had one report of a
criminal being killed by Kira.
-Wait, no one's been killed?
Really?
L (ON SPEAKER): Yes.
-I see.
So it's only a matter of time
before I'm convicted as Kira.
-What I wouldn't
give for an apple.
L (VOICEOVER):
What's going on here?
I thought the murders
would continue
even after Light was confined.
Instead, they've
stopped completely.
Light asked to be confined
in the first place.
If this continues, it'll
only strengthen the argument
that he is Kira.
The question left
will be whether or not
he was conscious of being Kira.
Does he really think
that's gonna work,
that he'll be let off
the hook if he can just
prove he wasn't
conscious of being Kira?
It's not like Light Yagami.
No, it's not like Kira.
-I can't take this anymore.
If I don't get an apple soon,
I don't know what-- [groans]
-In the end, I just have to get
through this, no matter what.
MISA: You know
what, Mr. Stalker?
Your video won't
sell if it's just me
sitting here the whole time.
L: Mr. Yagami looks pretty bad.
I think he's taking this
harder than Light or Misa.
MATSUDA: Well,
what do you expect?
It's been five days since
Light was put in prison.
And look, not a single criminal
who's name has been broadcast
was killed.
In these situations,
I think the parents
must suffer a lot
more than the accused.
AIZAWA: No kidding.
Especially now that we're
seeing proof that Light is Kira.
-Mr. Yagami?
-What is it?
Is it good news?
Is it bad news?
-No, I wanted to tell
you not to worry so much.
It doesn't matter
how much time you
devote to worrying about this.
The outcome will be the same.
This could go on
for quite some time.
Perhaps you should rest in
a more comfortable place.
-Impossible!
What makes you think
I care where I am?
It won't change anything.
With the state I'm in now,
this is the best place for me.
And no matter what the
result, when I leave here,
it's going to be with my son.
-I understand.
L (ON SPEAKER): Light, you've
only been here for one week,
but I'm sure it can't be easy.
Are you feeling all right?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Now
that I've come this far,
I think it's about time.
-Yeah, I know I must
look pretty bad in here.
But this useless
pride, I suppose
I'll have to get rid of it.
-Huh?
[grunting]
Got it.
Later.
-[gasps]
-Hm?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Why am I doing this?
I don't belong here.
-Ryuzaki, I realize that I was
the one pushing for confinement
and that I asked you
to put me in here,
but I just realized
something important.
This whole thing is
completely pointless.
-[together] Huh?
LIGHT (ON SPEAKER):
Because I'm not Kira!
You have to get me out of here.
-Hm.
I can't do that.
I promised you that no
matter what you said,
I wouldn't let you
out until I was
convinced that you are not Kira.
-Please, L. I wasn't
thinking clearly.
Do you really think
a serial killer
like Kira could
commit those crimes
without being aware of them?
If I have no memory of
his crimes, I'm not him.
-I've never been able
to accept this idea
that Kira has been acting
without self awareness
all this time.
But that doesn't change the
fact that all the evidence
point to you being Kira.
Since we imprisoned
you, Kira hasn't
committed a single murder.
-Listen, just hear me out.
I swear to you, I'm not lying.
You have to believe me.
I'm not Kira!
I must have been framed.
That's the only
explanation for this.
L (VOICEOVER): What's wrong
with you, Light, Yagami.
What you're saying
is completely absurd.
But for some reason, it
feels believable to me.
LIGHT: You have to let me out!
We're wasting time!
L (ON SPEAKER): We
can't let you out yet.
-Damn.
Why is this happening?
-What the hell is going on?
This isn't like Light at all.
He's contradicting himself.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
-Well, we can't release him now
that the murders have stopped.
It doesn't matter what he says.
I mean, even I know that much.
-Anyway, I don't care
what anyone says.
As far as I'm concerned, we
have all the proof we need.
Light Yagami is Kira,
and that's the end of it.
-What's going on?
I just heard.
Two weeks' worth of criminals
were just murdered all at once.
It happened yesterday.
-Yeah.
Kira is back.
-So did you guys
already tell the chief?
-No, not yet.
-Guess what, Chief?
Kira started killing again!
-What?
-It looks like Kira
was only resting.
But now he's started
punishing criminals again.
CHIEF YAGAMI (ON SPEAKER):
Is that true, Matsuda?
Then that means my son--
I shouldn't be happy
that people have been killed.
But at least Light's name
will finally be cleared.
Wait, knowing Ryuzaki, this
won't be enough to clear him.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Well, he's in the grey.
-Did you hear what
he just said, Chief?
CHIEF YAGAMI (ON
SPEAKER): Yeah, it's
a hell of a lot better than
being completely guilty,
thank god.
-I'm sure as greys go, he's a
shade closer to being cleared.
Let's tell Light!
L: Matsuda!
I mean, please
don't, Mr. Matsuda.
-Matsuda?
-We shouldn't tell
him about this.
-But-- but why not?
-Hello, Light.
-What is it, Ryuzaki?
-You've been here
just over two weeks
and not a single new
criminal has been punished.
Now, why make this
harder than it has to be?
Are you ready to confess?
LIGHT (ON SPEAKER):
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm telling you, you're wrong.
I understand why
you feel that way.
But even if the evidence does
point to me, I swear to you,
this is a set up.
I am not Kira!
Zoom in on me, if you want.
Go ahead, look at my eyes.
You tell me, do these look
like the eyes of someone
who is lying?
-Hm.
Amane, are you ready to
tell me who Kira is, or not?
-Huh?
That again?
I wish I knew, but I don't.
Because if I did, I'd
thank him for punishing
the burglar who
killed my parents.
To me, Kira is a hero.
L: I don't understand
what's going on here.
[theme music]
LIGHT: [laugh]
That-- that's crazy.
Wait, Dad.
If I die here, then the
truth will never be revealed!
Do you trust L more
than your own son?
Dad!