[theme music]
-Delete.
Delete!
NARRATOR: The average
Japanese adult
would say that Teru
Mikami was a child
with a strong sense of justice.
He was able to distinguish
right from wrong better
than any of his peers.
And compared to the
average Japanese person,
Teru had been through and
seen far worse miseries,
and even witnessed death.
[alarm beeping]
[giggling]
GIRL: His hat.
Get it.
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER):
In this world,
there is only good and evil.
That was one of the
first universal truths
I grasped from observing
the world around me
when I was a child.
Every human being,
without exception,
ends up falling into one
category or the other.
Even those in innocent years
of elementary school, one
could not escape that fact.
As class president, I strived
to achieve great things
for my fellow students, but
there were always enemies.
Good against evil.
-No!
Stop!
Let go of me, please!
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER): Evil
has to be confronted.
-What do you want, nerd?
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER):
There were times
when it seemed evil
would triumph over good.
But no matter what
happened to me,
I felt happy for one reason.
-Thank you, Teru.
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER): Hearing
those words of gratitude
from the victims made me want
to save them again and again.
For that reason, I
never spared any effort.
And in the end, I
was able to stand up
for my sense of justice.
[snickering]
-Does this bug you?
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER):
But that was only true
in the world of children.
Middle school was
another matter entirely.
The more I confronted evil,
the more enemies I had to face.
Victims would
become participants,
and even the people watching
would be influenced by evil
and become enemies themselves.
But for justice to triumph,
it requires action.
So I realized, to serve
justice, I had to delete evil.
The only person who understood
my hopes and remained my ally
was the woman who
raised me on her own.
My mother.
No.
Rather, it used to be my mother.
WOMAN: Teru, not
everything in the world
is going to work the
way you want it to.
You have to stop doing this.
There's no reason
for you to suffer
so much for your beliefs.
What do you think you're
proving getting hurt like this?
This is plain foolishness.
You have to do
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER):
My mother was wrong.
She didn't side with justice.
She was one of those who
deserved to be deleted.
That was when the
miracle happened.
Four of the worst
delinquents from my school
lost control of their car
while they were joyriding.
They died instantly.
One bystander was
killed as well.
That bystander was my mother.
In one fell swoop, all
the people I resented
had been deleted.
At first, I was terrified.
I couldn't stop shivering.
But then it hit me.
With these people
out of the picture,
how many others would
benefit as a result?
Clearly their victims
were relieved.
But beyond that.
Would'nt everyone in my class
be happier now that they were
gone?
And sure enough, I was right.
Our classroom became a
peaceful, joyful place.
There will always
consequences f evil deeds.
That is the way the world is.
The way it should be.
Evil must be deleted.
Now then, let's see.
Are there any more problems
with these records?
-No, they're fine.
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER):
With every passing year,
my commitment to justice
only grew stronger.
I saw that there
will always be those
who have no reason to exist.
Those whose very existence
is a threat to society.
And the closer they grew to
adulthood, the less likely
was that they would ever reform.
They could only be deleted.
Mysteriously, every time
I judged someone as evil,
they would soon
be taken care of.
Was it coincidence?
Was I special somehow?
In the end, it didn't matter.
Divine judgment must
be brought up evil.
And if it isn't, then someone
must take it upon themselves
to punish evil.
That's why I became
a prosecutor.
It is the role of
the prosecutor to see
that evil is brought to justice.
It was an ideal job for me.
And then God came before me.
Everything that had
been happening around me
wasn't coincidence.
It was divine justice.
God had been watching me.
God had seen how I did
not surrender to evil.
He reached out his
hand and punished
the evil people for me.
Once I realized that, I
started to frequent places
where God was bound
to be watching.
And then it happened.
God recognized me as
I had always hoped!
Not only that, but he found
me worthy of sharing his power
to eliminate evil!
With this, it doesn't matter
if I can't hear his voice.
I shall figure out what Kira
wants and carry out his will.
Delete.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Mikami made the choice
to kill Demegawa himself.
I never requested it.
An understandable move, but
now there's no spokesperson.
Kira needs a voice.
At the moment, I can't
make any moves myself.
What will he do?
-Kira isn't saying anything.
He must be in a situation
where he can't move freely.
But this is an
important time for him.
We need a spokesperson to
spread his word to the people.
Then I will take the initiative.
-Extra, extra!
There's a new development
in the Kira case.
He's chosen a new spokesperson
to take Demegawa's place.
Take a look.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): That woman.
Kiyomi Takada
-Good evening.
This is Kiyomi
Takada from News 6.
Starting today, it will be my
duty to spread the word of Kira
accurately and quickly.
From now on, NHN will fairly--
MATSUDA: So he picked
NHN's star newscaster, huh?
Kira's got good taste.
Choosing Taki was a good idea.
-(VOICEOVER) There's
no mistaking it.
That's the girl that
Light dated in university.
KIYOMI: --but also his liaison
with the people of the world.
-You've moved quickly, Mikami.
However, it won't
take them long to find
the connection between us,
which could be a problem.
No.
On second thought,
she's not a bad choice.
It's one I never would have
considered, since I already
knew her.
But this could actually
make things easier.
I can definitely
use her, but I'll
have to find a way
to contact her soon.
(VOICEOVER) Kiyomi Takada.
I had a chance to meet her when
I was part of a debate program
she was hosting.
She was a shrewd and fair
host for the most part,
but her attitude
changed suddenly
when Kira's name was mentioned.
She had a uniquely
rigid sense of justice
that I could identify with.
She hates crimes and social
evils with a passion.
I talked with her privately
several times after that.
She clearly supports Kira.
But it's more than that.
She thinks like Kira.
That makes her the
broadcaster most worthy
of being the new voice of Kira.
-(VOICEOVER) Kiyomi Takada.
It'd to be too
suspicious for Kira
to choose an ex-girlfriend
as his representative.
And there's been no sign of
Light sending her any messages.
Maybe I'm thinking
about this too much.
-Everyone, I just had an idea.
I was thinking we could
make use of Kiyomi Takada.
To be honest, I know her.
Back in university,
she and I were actually
dating for a little while.
-Whoa.
-(VOICEOVER) So he admits it.
He has no intention to
hide the connection.
-If she's acting as
his spokesperson,
she must be receiving
orders from him.
She's in contact
with Kira somehow.
I think our best bet is
to use that connection
to find a way to
Kira through her.
[growl]
MATSUDA: But Taki's
probably doing it
because Kira's
threatening her, right?
She might be too scared to help
us out with her investigation.
IDE: That's a good point.
-I'm not too worried about that.
I know her current
cell phone number.
I'm pretty sure that I'll
be able to convince her
once we get talking.
She'll meet with
me if I ask her to.
-Ha ha.
Wow.
Listen to this guy.
You're the man, Light.
-Talking to her will be
easy, but the real challenge
will be to get her to help
us find and arrest Kira.
We used to talk about a
lot of different topics
while we were in college,
and one thing was clear.
She worships Kira.
But we might be able to
use that to our advantage.
The police claim they
support Kira, but aren't
doing anything one
way or the other.
So I'll reveal that
I've joined the police,
and ask her what we can
do to help Kira further.
To her, it'll sound
like a good idea.
We can convince her to
assist us as long as we
pretend it's for Kira's benefit.
-Do you think
that'll go over well?
-I'm not entirely sure.
But it's worth a try, at least.
-I agree.
It'd be foolish for us to
pass up a lead like this.
-In that case, I'll
call her tonight.
AIZAWA: Light.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to listen
in on your conversation
with Ms. Takada.
-Of course.
That's fine with me.
Actually, it's better if you do.
If she lets slip
something about Kira,
it would be best if more
than one of us was listening.
-Uh-- yeah.
[phone ringing]
-Yes, Hello?
LIGHT: Kiyomi?
This is Light Yagami.
-Light?
Hi.
It's been a while.
What's going on?
-Kiyomi, I have something
important to tell you.
Could we meet somewhere?
I have a favor to ask you.
KIYOMI: A favor?
-Yeah.
I know my timing is pretty bad.
I mean, you're the woman the
whole world is watching right
now, so it might
not be possible.
-Don't play innocent and
humble with me, Light.
You wouldn't have
called if you didn't
think it was possible to see me.
LIGHT: You're right.
Ever since we graduated, I
wanted to talk to you again,
but I never had the chance.
And now it looks like our
jobs have brought us together.
After so much time, our paths
are about to cross again.
Call me crazy, but I
feel like this is fate.
-What do you mean, our jobs?
LIGHT: I'm working
with the police now.
That was part of what I
wanted to talk to you about.
In person.
-The police aren't
doing anything
to defy Kira at this point.
All right.
I may be able to
help you, depending
on what you're asking for.
-I appreciate it.
At the very least, I just want
you to hear what I have to say.
Anywhere.
Just us two.
-Well, OK then.
After tonight's
broadcast is finished.
-That sounds perfect.
I'll book a hotel room for us.
KIYOMI: A hotel room?
Are you sure?
The last I heard, you were
still living with Miss Amane.
Are things not going to
well on the home front?
LIGHT: Well, to
be honest, Misa's
just not intelligent
enough to be my partner.
MISA: Motchi.
-Yes?
-Your cooking is really good.
And I appreciate that you're
doing everything for me,
but it's been five days now.
-Right.
-Light doesn't know about you
hanging around all the time,
does he?
I'm beginning to get
a really bad feeling
about this whole thing.
-Uh-huh.
MISA: I mean, I know that
Light trusts me totally,
but don't you think
most people would
start saying I'm
cheating on him?
Oh, he'd be so jealous.
-Near and the others
told me that this woman
is supposed to be
the second Kira.
But it could really be this
unbelievably stupid girl?
-It seems that Kira still
hasn't tried to contact me yet.
If he's in a
situation where he's
unable to contact me
even if he wants to,
then the next best
thing would be for him
to contact Takada instead.
-Good evening, this
is the 9:00 news.
First, I have an announcement
that comes directly from Kira.
His words are to become
the new law of the world.
Kira will never
forgive those people
whose existence is
a threat to justice.
But he will also
not forgive those
who live wastefully, and
refuse to use their abilities
to contribute to the
betterment of society.
-What?
So Kira's going to
kill lazy people now?
-You're kidding me.
-(VOICEOVER) You're taking
this too far, Mikami.
It's too early to be making
those kinds of statements.
I've got to get a
hold of him soon.
-Matsuda, how is it?
-Good.
Audio and video
online, no blind spots.
-Until next time--
-The 9:00 news is just saying.
-Everything's in order.
I'll head back to HQ.
-OK.
[knocking]
-I missed you.
-Huh?
LIGHT: Um, I'm sorry.
It's just-- anyway,
please, sit down.
To be honest, it
doesn't seem like that
long since we last
saw each other.
-What the hell is Light doing?
He's not saying anything.
If he just stays silent,
she'll get suspicious.
-Come on.
Don't tell me you've never
been in love before, Ide.
-What?
-How's it going?
-The mood's perfect.
-That's not what I meant.
[buzzing]
-Huh?
-Please excuse me.
Kira.
(VOICEOVER) Is it Mikami?
-She just said it's Kira.
-Kira's contacting her directly?
-You should answer it.
-Um, right.
Hello.
No, I'm with a friend right now.
Yes, we're alone.
-(VOICEOVER) If
luck is on my side,
I can get on the phone myself.
Well, Mikami, can
you make it happen?
TAKADA: He wanted to
meet me all of a sudden.
-(VOICEOVER) Someone who
requests a private meeting with
Kira's spokesperson.
I'd like to speak
with him, if I may.
[gasp]
-He said the he wants
to speak to you.
-(VOICEOVER) Perfect.
I was right to
choose you, Mikami.
-She's passed the
phone to Light.
-It could be dangerous
if he's the real thing.
-Yes?
Hello?
MIKAMI (MODIFIED VOICE):
Who am I speaking to?
-Five pages on November 26th?
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
-You're God!
-(VOICEOVER) You're
doing well, Mikami.
Let's just see how much
you can figure out.
MIKAMI (MODIFIED VOICE): Got it.
You're not free to
speak right now.
-Yes.
MIKAMI (MODIFIED VOICE): You're
being watched at the moment.
-Yes.
But how can I trust
you're the real Kira?
MIKAMI (VOICEOVER): Is he asking
me to judge someone right now?
Turn to Sakura TV!
-What's that?
Sakura TV?
-Quick.
Let's check it out.
-We'll invite Kira back to our
program no matter what it might
take--
-He died!
IDE: This is bad.
He's the real thing.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Mikami.
You're even better
than I expected.
MATSUDA: What?
He's removing the bugs?
-We don't have a choice.
-I don't understand.
What's going on?
-Now I can talk without
any constraints.
-What?
-Listen, Kiyomi.
I am the real Kira.
That's right.
I'm Kira.
That's what I
wanted to tell you.
KIYOMI (VOICEOVER):
Light is Kira?
-Listen.
I won't allow you to
ask Kiyomi who I am.
You don't need to
know my identity.
-Yes.
I'll leave the rest to you, God.
-Do you understand?
I am Kira.
The man who was on the
phone is one of my followers
who I've shared my power with.
-I-- I can't believe it's you.
You were the only man
I ever really admired.
To be honest, the only man I
ever felt a connection with.
And now to find you're
Kira-- it's incredible.
-Please, join me,
Kiyomi, and you
will be the goddess
of the New World.
-Oh, Light.
[phone ringing]
-Light, are you OK?
-Yeah.
Kiyomi was able to work
things out with Kira.
I've decided that
from now on, I'm
going to pretend
to be dating her.
We might be able to
find Kira that way.
-Delete.
Delete.
Delete Delete.
Delete!
[theme music]
LIGHT: Come to think
of it, it's always
been a one on one
battle between myself
and L. It's been going
on since the beginning.
Alright, Near.
Fine.
I'll come out if you come out.
I'll accept your challenge.