[theme music]
-I feel you're the first
friend that I have ever had.
-Whoa.
-Hm.
-Misa?
-Yes?
-Then could you
ask Rem to kill L?
-Huh?
-Rem, I want Light to love me.
And I know we could
be happy together.
It's all I ever wanted.
-That's fine.
I'll kill L for you.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): L will die.
That's all it took.
REM: So when should I kill him?
-[gasp]
-If you take them to where he
is, I can kill him immediately.
LIGHT: The sooner the better.
Maybe tomorrow.
Hm.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I should think this
through before we do anything.
-I need tonight to decide
how we're going to kill L.
And I'll give you
my answer tomorrow.
REM: Very well.
LIGHT: Also, no matter
what, you can't kill him
until I give the order.
No matter what.
Understood?
REM: All right.
I'll promise you that, at
least where L is concerned.
-Misa, I need you to give
me your cell phone number.
-About time.
What took you so long?
Give me yours too, OK?
-No, Misa.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
-Why not?
I'm your girlfriend.
I should have your number.
-I already told you, I'm under
surveillance by the police.
Keep in mind, it's
not difficult for them
to bug even
cellphones these days.
MISA: Oh, OK.
Then what about this?
I'll just give you
one of my phones.
I ended up with
three of them, 'cause
I use them for different things.
-Yeah, good idea.
If we use yours, I
think we'll be safe.
MISA: That's great!
I can hear your voice
everyday, and text you, too.
-No, I'll keep this
one turned off.
I'll be the only one
making the calls,
and only when it's
absolutely necessary.
-What?
No way.
Then when are you gonna call me?
-Probably tomorrow.
-Oh.
-That will most likely
be the day we execute L,
but I'll call you either way.
-What?
Tomorrow?
It doesn't sound like
a very romantic call,
but I suppose we can always
talk about us afterwards.
-Well, I think you should
probably go home now, Misa.
MISA: Huh?
But why?
It's only 7 o'clock.
The time for lovers is
just beginning, you know?
We can go for a romantic
dinner, then maybe a moonlight
stroll in the park.
And after that, the
main event! [giggle]
LIGHT: Misa.
-Huh?
[gasp]
RYUK: [laugh] Wow.
-Listen, you have
to go home now.
-OK.
Also,
- when you're talking
to Rem outside,
be careful that no
one's around to listen.
Just whisper.
That's what I
always do with Ryuk.
MISA: OK.
Bye-bye.
Have a good night.
-Bye-bye, Misa!
Come again real soon!
RYUK: [laugh] That kiss
came out of nowhere.
LIGHT: Sure.
It's very important that Misa
stays infatuated with me.
-Oh.
-More importantly,
I need to decide
if L should die tomorrow.
Since he hasn't gone
public yet, if Ryuga dies,
the other task force members
will be suspicious of me.
So I have to make
sure I'm prepared.
-I see.
I thought perhaps
you were hesitating
because he said he thinks
of you as a friend.
-[laugh] A friend?
I just gave him what he wanted.
From the start, I've said if
it's my friendship he wants,
I'd give it to him as
a way to win his trust.
Ryuga and Light Yagami
appear to be friends.
But L is Kira's enemy.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): That's right.
Ryuga revealed that he is
L. Therefore, he must die.
If I have him die
in an accident,
chances are that less people
will suspect I'm Kira.
And even if they do,
there'd be no proof.
I can only speculate what
will happen after he dies.
Tomorrow will be
L's, or at least
Ryuga and Ryuzaki's,
last day alive.
-Hair.
Hm.
Snack crumbs.
Hair.
Mr. Yagami?
Huh?
L: If I die within the next
few days, your son is Kira.
Hm, another hair.
--[gasp] What did you
just say, Ryuzaki?
-Exactly.
What are you talking
about, anyway?
-If anything happens
to me, I've asked
Watari to make himself
available to you.
So I'm counting on the team.
-Ryuzaki, you said he was
almost cleared, and now this?
Honestly, how much do
you suspect my son?
L: Hm.
The truth is, I don't even
what to think anymore.
I've never been in a
situation like this.
If Kira and the second Kira
are working together right now,
things are not
looking good for me.
Given that, I may
not be thinking
as clearly as I normally
do, so I could be wrong.
Maybe I still
consider him a suspect
only because we don't
have anyone else.
But still, if I do
happen to be killed soon,
please assume that
your son is Kira.
[gasping]
L (VOICEOVER): I have no choice
but to make a sneak attack.
This is all a wager now.
LIGHT: [laugh] I
wouldn't say that.
I just know how to get
by, that's all. [gasp]
-Hey, what's wrong?
-Ah.
Hey, Light!
How's it going?
-Kiyomi, can we
continue this later?
I need a moment alone with him.
-Uh, OK.
-I hope she's not upset.
-Never mind that.
Is it OK to be here?
Didn't you say you were
afraid to appear in public?
-Yeah, I did.
But then I realized that
as long as you're not Kira,
I should be safe.
The fact is, you're the only
one on the outside who knows me
as L. In the unlikely event
that I die in the next few days,
I've instructed your father
and everyone at headquarters
to assume that you are Kira?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Damn him.
-Besides, you told me yourself
that you missed having me
around at school, so
I figured, why not
come back for a
little change of pace?
As long as it doesn't kill
me, college is a lot of fun.
LIGHT: I have to admit,
without you around,
intelligent conversation
is hard to come by.
L: [laugh] I see.
Luckily, Kyomi's there
to fill the void.
LIGHT: Well,
something like that.
-[laughs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Oh, now I don't know.
Is it still OK to
kill him today?
No, as soon as I make
the decision to kill him,
he suddenly appears, almost as
if to distract me from my goal.
I guess he's trying to
guarantee his safety.
And the way things are, I'm
playing right into his hands.
-Hey, do you want to have some
cake with me in the cafeteria?
-Sure.
I have a break now anyway.
-Mm.
That's perfect.
I'm kind of craving
shortcake right now.
-Well, let's hope they have it.
MISA: Light, there you are!
[giggle] I had a photo shoot
nearby, so I thought
I'd come by to see you.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Misa, you idiot.
-Oh, this must be
a friend of yours.
He looks so different, unique.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Wait, I've won.
Misa will be able to
see Ryuga's real name.
MISA: Hi, there.
I'm Light's
girlfriend, Misa Amane.
Nice to meet you.
-I'm Hideki Ryuga.
-Huh?
Hideki Ryuga--
-Yeah, he has the exact
same first and last name
as the famous idol.
Pretty bizarre, huh?
MISA (VOICEOVER): But it's
different than the name
I'm seeing.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Ryuga, deciding
to come here today
was a mistake.
-[gasp]
-[laughs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Why
the hell is he laughing?
Could it mean he
knows something?
It makes no sense.
If he somehow guessed that
she's the second Kira,
there's no way he'd
be laughing right now.
L: Light, you're a lucky guy?
-Huh?
L: I have been huge
fan of yours ever
since the August
issue of "Eighteen."
-What?
Really?
That's so sweet of you?
-Hey.
Oh, my god.
Isn't that girl Misa Misa?
-You're right.
It's her.
Oh, she's so cute.
-Oh, wow.
I should have guess I'd be
spotted with all these kids
around.
-I'm, like, your biggest fan.
-Keep up the good work.
-Oh, thank you.
Couldn't do it without you.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): What is this?
-No way!
Somebody just touched my butt.
-Uh.
This is an outrage!
Taking advantage of this
situation is unforgivable.
I will find whoever is
responsible for this.
-[giggle] Oh, Ryuga.
You're so funny.
[laughter]
MAN: I want to touch her, too.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I want to
ask Misa what L's real name is
as soon as possible, but all
these people are in the way.
-Misa, it's time.
Or were you planning
to be late again?
-No, I'm-- I'm sorry, Yoshi.
YOSHI: Let's go.
MISA: O-- OK.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Perfect.
Now that Misa's
away from the crowd,
I just have to give her a call
and ask for L's real name.
-Bye, Light.
I'll see you after
I'm done work.
Miss you already. [giggle]
-Now, then.
Perhaps we should get going.
-Yeah.
Actually, could you go on ahead?
I need to go use the restroom.
-Oh, OK, then.
I'll see you there.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): It's over.
It's been fun, L. I'm
grateful that I was the one
to discover your name, so
I could kill you myself.
L, it's been fun.
I'm grateful that I was the
one to discover your name,
so I could kill you myself.
[phone ringing]
[ringtone]
-Yes?
Hello?
-What do you mean, hello?
-Oh, is that you, Light.
I guess must have dropped this
phone in all of the commotion
earlier on.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): He took it.
Bastard.
-Uh, hello?
LIGHT (ON PHONE): Yeah, that's--
that's Misa's cell phone you
have.
I can give it back to her.
-Oh, I see.
Sure, that makes sense.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Ryuga, he probably thinks
he's pretty clever right now.
But Misa has another phone
he doesn't know about.
I'll just call that one instead.
[phone ringing]
L: Oh.
Oh, this time's it's actually
my cell phone. [clears throat]
Yes?
Yes, I see.
So it's done then?
I understand.
I'm not exactly sure
how you'll take this,
but regarding Misa
Amane, there's
something you should know.
We've taken her into
custody under suspicion
of being the second Kira.
RYUK: [laughs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): How long
has he known about Misa?
I never thought he'd
find her this quickly.
-We gathered physical
evidence from the envelopes
that were sent by
the second Kira.
In particular, we
recovered hairs and fibers
from the masking tape
used to seal them.
They matched what we
found in Misa's room.
There would be a public
uproar if it gets out
that she's been apprehended
as the second Kira.
So officially, we've charged her
manager with drug possession,
and she's a voluntary witness.
But I doubt any of
this will get out.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I was careless.
The videos-- I should have
destroyed all the evidence
before the police had a
chance to go through it.
In the end, Ryuga knew
that his best defense
was to stay close to me,
rather than trying to hide.
He confronted things head on.
This wager was my--
L (VOICEOVER): Was my--
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Was my-- [gasp]
-Hm?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Not yet.
The real battle is
just beginning, L.
-Watari, has she
said anything yet?
WATARI (ON SPEAKER): No,
she hasn't spoken a word.
L: Get me a visual
of her, will you?
WATARI (ON SPEAKER):
Are you sure?
L: Yes.
And quickly.
[gasping]
[crying]
MAN: Ryuzaki, what's
the meaning of this?
L: I've Apprehended
her on suspicion
of being the second Kira.
I'm afraid thinks is necessary.
-Chances are, Amane is guilty.
There seems to be enough
evidence to convict her.
But all the same.
-Yes, there can be no mistake.
Now we need a
confession out of her.
We need to know how she
kills, whether she knows Kira,
and if so, who he really is.
Watari, take the
necessary precautions.
But beyond that, you're free to
do whatever has to be done, OK?
Just make her speak.
WATARI (ON SPEAKER): Very well.
L: Oh, and Mr. Yagami?
-Huh?
L: Light has now become
our prime suspect.
And I'm probably going to
bring him in for interrogation
as well.
Please be prepared for that.
WATARI (ON SPEAKER):
Ryuzaki, Amane is talking.
-Huh?
Quickly, get me a
visual and audio.
[grunt]
MAN: Finally, after
three days of this, huh?
[crying] I-- I can't
take it anymore.
Kill me.
-Huh?
-Kill me.
Please just kill me.
-I don't know.
Maybe this was all too much
for a young girl to take.
-He's right.
We've pushed her too far.
ROBOT: Misa Amane,
can you hear me?
-I hear you.
Please, just kill me now.
-Does this mean you admit
to being the second Kira?
Is this the reason
you wish to die.
-No.
I don't know anything
about the second Kira.
I really can't
take this anymore.
I'd rather be dead.
Now hurry up and kill me!
If you wanted to, you could
kill me right now, couldn't you?
-Misa, do you mean--
-Yes.
Kill me.
-Do you really mean that, Misa?
-Yes, I do.
[sigh] I can't take it anymore.
Kill me.
-If I do this, then
Light Yagami dies, too.
This is all his fault.
-You can't.
No, you can't.
Please, just kill me.
-Why, Misa?
Why do you want to die for him?
MISA: Fine!
If you won't kill me--
-Stop her!
Watari, don't let
her bite her tongue.
[muffled yelling]
-Is it possible
that this behavior
could be attributed
to Kira controlling
her actions before death?
-Oh, what's the matter, Rem?
-Light Yagami, Misa
has refused my offer
to help her escape, no
doubt because she knows
it would cause you trouble,
since the police would then
have proof of her powers.
When her suffering became
more than she could bear,
she started begging
me to kill her.
All of this because she
wants you to love her.
I could not possibly
let it go on like that.
I couldn't bring
myself to do it.
There was only one way to
save her from her suffering.
-Forfeiting ownership
of the Death Note.
-Yes.
If Misa forfeits ownership
of the Death Note,
all her memories related
to it would disappear.
All the murders she
committed with it, the fact
that you are Kira-- all
those memories would be gone.
Your secret would be safe.
Also, Misa would no longer be
able to Ryuk or me, either.
Misa, when this is done,
you'll forget everything
about Shinigami
and the Death Note.
-[whimpering]
-It's OK.
The human being who you
love is Light Yagami.
I promise those
feelings will remain.
So Misa, forfeit ownership
of the Death Note,
and leave everything
to Light Yagami.
-Mhm.
-Huh?
Hm.
-And so Misa is no longer
the owner of a Death Note.
-You did the right thing, Rem.
I was beginning
to think that was
the only way out
of this situation.
If her memories
of the Death Note
are gone, than
chances are, they'll
have to release her eventually.
-Light Yagami, I
proposed this to Misa,
knowing it was exactly
what you wanted
and that it would
serve your purposes.
But I did so on one condition.
And that is, if you don't
save Misa, I will kill you.
-I understand.
And I have a pretty good
idea what L will do next.
I have a plan.
This is goodbye, Ryuk.
Huh?
[theme music]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Yeah, I know
I must look pretty bad in here.
But this useless
pride, I suppose
I'll have to get rid of it.