[theme music]
HIGUCHI (ON PHONE):
And once you're
fully convinced I'm
the real thing, you
and I can get married.
-And so, based on what
he said, Higuchi is Kira!
L (VOICEOVER): If the killing
of criminals stops now,
then there's no
doubt that Higuchi
is the one with Kira's powers.
However, I know Amane would
do almost anything for Light.
But to think that she
would actually go this far?
If criminals do stop
dying after this,
it will make it difficult to
determine a critical element,
how Kira conducts his murders.
I have to think of a plan.
-Misa.
How did you get
Higuchi to confess?
-Easy.
That guy's totally
in love with me.
All I had to do was
tell him I'd marry him
if he was really Kira.
Plus, I managed to convince
him that I'm the second Kira.
If I didn't say this
now, I'd probably
end up contradicting
my story later.
-Misa.
You idiot!
Didn't I tell you
to deny all that?
-But-- But now we know
Higuchi's Kira, right?
So what's the problem?
Can't we just catch him?
-I suppose this is what you
would call a victory, right
Matsuda?
-But right now, we
still don't know
exactly how he kills
his victims, do we?
-Yes.
That's what I was thinking.
Before we move to
arrest Higuchi,
I want to find out
how he kills people.
-If the criminals stop dying, we
won't be able to figure it out,
unless we come up
with another idea.
Isn't that right?
-Yes.
At any rate, even if
we do arrest Higuchi,
we're not going to
do it until we're
certain that criminals
have stopped dying.
Let me think about
this for a moment.
Wedy.
WEDY (ON COMPUTER): Yeah.
-An update on the current
situation, please.
WEDY (ON COMPUTER):
Everything's going smoothly.
We should be able to track
70% of their movements
using our cameras inside
the office building.
-What about outside the office?
-That's not gonna be possible
with just Watari and me.
-What if you focus
solely on Higuchi?
-Higuchi?
I've only been able to enter
the houses of five of the men
so far, but Mido,
Namikawa, and Higuchi all
have super high tech security
systems, especially Higuchi.
He recently constructed
a dampening room
that shuts out any
electronic waves.
It took me two days just
to break into the place.
-This guy sure does
sound suspicious.
-Hm.
All right.
Then begin installing
microphones, trackers,
and cameras, but
not in the house.
Instead, just put
them in every car.
WEDY (ON COMPUTER): What?
After getting this far?
Do you know how difficult it is
to break into someone's house?
Besides, do you have any idea
of how many cars this guy has?
-(MUMBLING) He has six.
WEDY (ON COMPUTER): Fine then.
I just have to install them
in all his cars, right?
-Yes, thank you.
MISA (VOICEOVER): If Higuchi
had been bugged earlier,
I would have been
in big trouble.
-Light.
I'm sorry to keep coming
back to this topic.
I'll just get
right to the point.
-What is it?
-Do you remember?
Killing anyone, I mean?
-Huh?
Are you still going about that?
Look, I'm not Kira!
How many times do I--
-I just want you to
answer the question.
Well, do you remember?
-No, I don't.
-Miso, what about you?
-I don't remember.
How could I, 'cause
I'm not Kira.
Look, Light.
Please listen to what
I'm about to say.
I'd like you to thoroughly
analyze my current theory.
This could determine the way in
which we end up catching Kira.
Light Yagami used to be Kira.
Kira's power has somehow
passed onto another person.
Light Yagami now has no
memory of ever being Kira.
I need your analysis based
on these assumptions.
Do you think you
can do that for me?
-Yeah.
I'll give it a try.
-Light Yagami used to be Kira.
Kira's power has somehow
passed onto another person.
Was that because Light
Yagami wanted it to happen,
or was there someone
else in control
of Light, lurking in
the background, who
gave him the power?
Was it that person who passed
Light's powers to someone else?
-Given your premise,
it would be my will.
-Yes, of course.
If there is a third
party with the ability
to bestow or
transfer Kira's power
and they didn't want their
method to be discovered,
it makes no sense that
they would wait so long
to transfer it from
you to the next Kira.
If we believe that this was the
work of some being watching us
from above, then
we'd have to accept
that they are
impossible to catch, not
to mention I'd already be dead.
Or at the very
least, I'm being made
to be a fool by
eternally dancing
in the palm of someone's hand.
It's highly unlikely
that such a being exists.
Even if Light Yagami
was Kira, Kira's power
can be transferred by the will
of the person who possesses it.
Thank you, Light.
I can now say that
I feel 99% better.
[music playing]
-We'll create a
situation where Higuchi
won't be able to pass off
his power to anyone else.
We'll have him show
us how he kills.
-So, what are you gonna do?
-I'm going to trick
Higuchi using Sakura TV.
-Like a hidden camera show!
WOMAN: What?
L: We'll use the Kira special
that Demegawa airs every week.
We'll book a three
hour timeslot.
It'll be announced that
Kira's identity will
be revealed near the
end of the special.
-Would anyone actually
buy that, though?
This is Sakura TV after all.
For all we know, Higuchi might
not even watch that program.
-We'll get Namikawa to call
him and say, this is bad.
Turn on your TV.
That should be enough
to get him watching.
Higuchi will buy
it once he realizes
that the special guest on TV is
someone who knows his secret.
-Oh, I get it.
So we'll be using Aiber, then.
He'll reveal that he
was a spy all along!
-No, I'm afraid
you're incorrect.
We will not be using Aiber.
Whoever appears on
the show has to be
someone who Higuchi believes
he'll be able to kill.
In other words, it
has to be someone
whose name he can
look up easily.
-But we're never going to find
a person like that, are we?
-Hm.
-You're the only
one who can do it.
MISA: Matsu!
-Matsu?
-Higuchi probably thinks
that you were listening in
on their meeting and overheard
their plan to kill people.
It would make sense that Misa's
manager who he thought was dead
is the one revealing his secret.
-That's right.
We'll have Sakura TV use
a voice filter and frosted
glass to protect your identity.
Higuchi will probably
realize from the announcement
and the silhouette that it's
the manager, Taro Matsui.
And just to make sure, we'll
have the studio mess up
and accidentally
reveal your face
from behind the frosted glass.
-Wow!
That sounds exciting!
L: Until the show
ends, the announcer
will keep saying they'll
reveal the full name of H,
who's acting as Kira.
-Higuchi would feel cornered.
He'd have no choice but to find
out the manager's name as soon
as possible.
We can anticipate what
actions he'll take.
-We'll witness his
killing method.
After that, we arrest him.
There is one potential
problem with this plan.
If Higuchi can kill by simply
looking at someone's face,
just like the second
Kira, Matsuda will die.
-But, considering the fact
that you're still alive,
and how he's pursuing Misa,
I doubt that's the case.
-At any rate, we're
only going to do this
once criminals stop dying.
We'll have to wait
for two or three
days to see whether
or not that happens.
In the meantime,
Matsuda will have
to decide if he wants to
go through with this plan.
-I don't need two or
three days to decide.
I want to do this.
-Well, I'm here.
What's with this
private meeting?
-Namikawa.
Tell me, who do
you think is Kira?
-Ha.
Why do you want to
know what I think?
Besides, for all I know,
it could be you, Shimura.
Or maybe even Mido.
-Shimura can't be Kira.
He was the one who came
crying to me about how
he can't go along with
Kira's crimes anymore.
-Really?
But if Mido had
turned out to be Kira,
you would have been killed.
-No.
You and Mido would have
been successful on your own.
There's no way
either of you would
need to hold those
stupid meetings.
Let alone with seven others.
I can at least see that much.
We're all cooperating
with these killings
because we're afraid
of Kira turning on us.
I mean, it's only
a matter of time
to until the public finds out.
And this isn't going to
stop until that happens.
-So, Shimura, let
me ask you, then,
who do you think Kira might be?
-Takahasi or Higuchi.
-No.
Takahashi is just a decoy.
Kira would make sure there are
people less clever than him.
-Well, then, it looks like we
all know the truth already.
It's Higuchi, isn't it?
-Yes.
He's the one who's the
most obsessed with money
and success.
He might always act as if he's
not interested in those things,
but that just proves
it all the more.
-And he always insults
everyone around him,
and can't use his people well.
I believe that's
why he was demoted
from being head of the
development department.
By the way, I meant to ask-- was
I the only one you invited her?
-I also invited
Ooi, but he said you
can hold your stupid private
meetings by yourself.
Go figure.
-Heh.
Good old Ooi, always
the blunt one.
-We can also rule out Kida
as a possible suspect,
as he was the one who provided
the account for funds in order
to commission Coil.
-Namikawa.
During that first meeting
after Hatori died,
you got a call on
your cell phone.
I was wondering who it was from.
-You know, Shimura, you
really are a sharp one.
Kira probably selected
you because he
appreciates your caution.
[phone ringing] Hm.
Namikawa speaking.
-It's L. Before I go
on, are you by yourself?
-No.
LIGHT (ON PHONE): Then just act
like it's a normal call again.
-I don't think there's
any need for that.
One of the people
here with me was just
expressing his suspicions
about your last phone call.
-Who is that on the line?
Namikawa?
-It's L. L, Mido and
Shimura are here as well.
I'm reasonable certain that
neither of them are Kira.
In fact, they seem fed
up with it at this point.
I'll speak for them
and say they'll
choose to stand back and watch
your face-off with Kira, like I
plan to.
-That's fine.
Tonight, I'm gonna catch Kira.
But I'll need a favor from you.
-Hm?
Then it's the end for Higuchi.
-What?
You know that it's him?
-Ha!
So even the great
L can be tricked.
Based on your reaction,
I'm now 100% certain
that Higuchi is Kira.
-Namikawa's pretty smart, huh?
But then, I always thought he
was, from looking at his face.
I guess this proves it.
-No.
That was just because
Light messed up.
-I'm baiting Higuchi with a
staged TV special tonight.
Sakura TV.
A few minutes into the program,
I want you to contact Higuchi,
tell him to tune in.
Do that for me, and
I won't go after you,
or any of the other five.
As for the others,
Kida, Takahasi, and Ooi,
if they try to do anything,
make sure to stop them.
-All right.
I understand.
It seems it really was Higuchi.
He'll be captured tonight.
Apparently.
[laughter]
-It's been about
three days since I
stopped killing criminals.
That should be good
enough, shouldn't it?
Now, when I marry Misa
Amane, the second Kira,
I'll have the Shinigami eyes.
With that power in
my hands, Yotsuba
will be under my control.
[laughter]
[phone ringing]
-Higuchi, we've got a problem.
Turn on the television.
Check out Sakura TV.
-Hm?
-So you're saying one of
those people is Kira, right?
-(MODIFIED VOICE) Yes.
I've got a lot of
evidence to prove it, too.
-What the hell is this?
Come in, it's probably a hoax.
This is Sakura TV.
-No, it's more than that.
At the beginning
of the show he said
that he overheard a meeting.
Between eight people.
-What?
Someone who knows
about the meetings?
Who is it?
Did someone betray us?
-(MODIFIED VOICE) Then one
of them was killed by Kira,
and now there are
only seven left.
The man who died was Mr. H.
-(VOICEOVER) Mr. H?
Hatori.
If he knows this much, he
could be one of the other six.
No, maybe it's Coil.
(MODIFIED VOICE) Mr. H wanted
to leave the meetings, and was
killed by Kira because of that.
-(VOICEOVER) No, it can't
be any of the others.
There's no benefit
for them to do this.
But no one else knows about
the meetings, do they?
Dammit, who is it?
What?
Wait.
Could it be--
-Huh?
Oh!
Ah!
-It's-- it's him!
-Cover him up!
Cover him up!
-It's Misa's manager.
Matsui.
That's his name.
Why is he still alive?
NAMIKAWA (ON
PHONE): He explained
earlier that he thought
he was going to be killed.
He pretended to fall out
of the apartment window
and escaped to a balcony
a few floors below.
-(VOICEOVER) But that can't be.
Just to be careful, I
went home that night
and wrote his name
in the notebook
like it was written
on his business card.
Why is he still alive, then?
Could he be a former
entertainer who
became a manager
using his stage name?
Is that possible?
-If that weren't
bad enough, he said
that he continued to investigate
Yotsuba up until now,
and he's figured out
which one of us is Kira.
I'm contacting everyone
right now to let them now.
-All right.
We'll talk later.
MAN (ON TV): Sir, we're terribly
sorry for that accident.
Are you all right?
We can stop, if you want.
-(MODIFIED VOICE) No.
I knew I was gonna be in
danger going into this.
This is for the sake
of justice, so I'll
see it through to the end,
even if it means my death.
-Yeah, that's perfect.
Listen, just be sure to hold
off on the Kira announcement
until the last
minute, all right?
-I have to kill him!
Calm down.
Misa knows his face, so
if she's the second Kira,
she should know what
his real name is.
[phone ringing]
-It's him.
[beeping]
-Oh, what the hell?
-(MODIFIED VOICE) To be honest,
I've been debating for a long
time whether or not I should
make this announcement.
But now that I'm
here, I know I've
done the right thing
in coming forward.
-This is bad.
Who knows then he'll
make the announcement?
MAN (ON TV): Kira's identity
will be announced soon.
[phone ringing]
WOMAN (ON TV): Cosme
Misa, a devilish charm.
An angel's glitter.
Misa's new line of
lipstick, just for you.
-Mido, it's me.
Are you watching Sakura TV?
Why don't you call your father
in the House of Counselors?
Have him pull some strings
at the Ministry of Internal
Affairs to stop this broadcast.
-I'm watching, but I don't
think we could stop it.
No one believes this
program, so we'd only
make ourselves look
suspicious if we stop it.
Besides, there shouldn't
be anything to worry about.
The guy revealed
his face earlier.
Everyone knows it's
really Taro Matsui.
Namikawa's already gone
ahead and told everyone
to watch the show.
Since one of us
seven has to be Kira,
that should mean Taro
Matsui will soon be dead.
Right?
-(VOICEOVER) Of course.
I'm the only one who
knows, or even suspects
that Taro Matsui
isn't his real name.
That means if I
say anything, it'll
reveal the fact that I'm Kira.
Yeah.
It's true.
I'll talk to you later.
-Stay tuned to Sakura TV.
-Dammit!
WATARI: Ryuzaki.
Mogi is in position in front
of Yoshida productions.
He's just received
a call from Higuchi.
-Yes, it's time for phase two.
Everything's as planned.
HIGUCHI: Moji.
Where's Misa?
MOJI: Oh, Mr. Higuchi.
Pleasure to hear from you.
I'm sorry, but Misa Misa's
taking a much needed vacation
right now.
She should be back by, oh,
tomorrow morning, though.
You can reach her then.
HIGUCHI: I'm asking
you where she is now.
MOJI: Well, that's
private information.
She's requested that no
one know where she is.
I'm very sorry.
I'll have her contact you
tomorrow, first thing.
-(VOICEOVER) Damn!
I know his face.
I could kill him at any time,
if only I knew his name.
Do you know if
Misa's former manager
was an entertainer
at some point?
-Come again?
HIGUCHI (ON PHONE): I'm
talking about Taro Matsui!
-Oh.
I was only recently hired, so
I don't know much about him.
If you need some
information, I can
let you talk to someone
from the office.
I just remembered.
Everyone's in Okinawa
at the moment.
You could try calling
the president, though.
-This is going
exactly as I planned.
It's almost scary.
-You shouldn't be scared, Light.
You should be happy.
WATARI: I'm patching
you in to Higuchi's call
with the president of
Yoshida Productions.
HIGUCHI: This is
Higuchi from Yotsuba.
That manager's real name
isn't Taro Matsui, is it?
-He's not even
pretending to hide
what he's asking
about now, is he?
Stupid Higuchi.
-If he's acting like that, it's
proof he's beginning to panic.
-Then what was his real name?
PRESIDENT (ON PHONE):
I think it Yamada.
No.
Wait.
Yamashida.
Yeah.
And his first name was--
I'm sorry, I can't remember.
-Don't screw with me!
Why the hell can't you remember
the names of the people you
hire!?
PRESIDENT (ON PHONE): All right.
No need for that
kind of language.
I've got his personnel
file back at the office.
-Then go back there and get it.
PRESIDENT (ON PHONE):
You gotta be kidding me.
Give me a break.
We're on our first company
vacation in two years!
If you wanna know
that badly, I'll
give you the pin code
for the office lock.
You can go in yourself
and look it up.
How's that?
The personnel files are in the
desk in the back to the left.
You'll find them filed
in the bottom drawer.
They should all be
sorted alphabetically.
But I'm pretty sure
it was Yamashida.
-(VOICEOVER) If they're going
to announce it at the end
of the program, that
means I have two hours.
-So what's he gonna do?
-I see Higuchi.
He's only carrying a single bag.
I'm in pursuit.
-Everything's still
going according to plan.
-Yes.
-(VOICEOVER) I'll kill him.
I'll kill him no matter what.
I've come this far.
I won't let them stop me.
I'm not giving up until
I have everything.
[maniacal laughter]
[theme music]
HIGUCHI: With these
eyes, I'm invincible!
MAN: Higuchi has a gun on him!
The chief has been shot.
MISA: This isn't
sounding very good.
CHIEF YAGAMI: Higuchi.
Hold it right there.
DEMEGAWA: With this
show, I'm gonna
have 100% ratings for sure!
HIGUCHI: I made it in time.