[HIYORI]
Help us!
Please! Yato needs you!
[KOFUKU]
Ya--
[DAIKOKU grunts]
[DAIKOKU]
Border!
[HIYORI shrieks]
[YUKINE]
A Borderline?
[HIYORI groans]
Take it down!
Please let us in!
Daikoku!
Kofuku!
Don't just stand there!
Can't you see?
[HIYORI]
Yato's going to die!
[HIYORI sobbing]
[DAIKOKU] You're the only one
I'm letting inside.
[HIYORI gasps]
[DAIKOKU]
Kofuku.
Can you purify Hiyori
and cleanse her blight?
[KOFUKU]
Right.
[water spraying]
[KOFUKU]
This water's pure.
It's pumped in directly
from the spring in the garden.
Come over here
and wash your body.
[HIYORI] What
about Yato?
It's too late for Yatty's
blight to be cleansed now.
It can't be!
How?
Yuki...
He needs
to be punished.
[YATO moaning]
[DAIKOKU]
Kofuku.
Take over
for a while.
I'm gonna visit
some nearby shrines.
[HIYORI]
What?
Why do you
need to do that?
What is Yukine's
punishment?
He needs ablution.
Huh?
An ablution's a ceremony
for expelling blight.
But it requires three
Regalias to pull it off.
So we'll need two
more besides me.
[KOFUKU]
Just to be clear here.
You know what'll happen
if the ablution fails.
You do, right?
[DAIKOKU]
Yeah.
Regardless...
We need the other
Regalias here right away.
[YATO whimpering]
[DAIKOKU] He doesn't
look like he'll even last
until the morning.
[DAIKOKU]
Yukine.
Take one step from where you're
standing and I will kill you.
[YUKINE]
Yeah, whatever.
[clothes rustling]
[car sputtering]
[car roaring]
[HIYORI]
That's cold!
[water spraying]
[HIYORI] Yato is
seriously on the verge of death.
But what exactly are they going
to do to punish Yukine?
[water spraying]
[HIYORI]
Please.
Please, please.
Just let them both be okay.
Actually...
[HIYORI] I never really
thought about it but,
Who does help gods and Regalias?
[TENJIN]
Yato's truly dying?
[DAIKOKU]
Yes.
[REGALIAS gasping]
[AYU]
An actual ablution?
[MOYU] If you don't
do it correctly,
you can get eaten
by a Phantom.
[MIYU]
What?
Are you serious?
[NAYU] I had a friend
who took part in one.
It was a serious ablution
and she helped out.
[MIYU] What happened
to her?
Is she okay?
I don't know.
Nobody has seen her
since it took place.
[ALL gasp]
[MAYU] If you'll
permit it.
I can help.
[AYU]
Hey, hold on!
You aren't serious, are you?
[MAYU] Yato did grant me
the name Tomo at one time.
[DAIKOKU]
Thank you.
And who are...?
Mayu, now.
We only need
one more, then.
[ALL whimper]
I greatly appreciate
your assistance.
I ask no more.
You've been generous enough.
[DAIKOKU] Please try not
to fret over this.
Worrying would only affect Lord
Tenjin's health.
[car roaring]
[TSUYU]
My Lord.
[TENJIN sighs]
Yato's been corrupted.
How could that fool
allow this?
What is he doing?
[DAIKOKU]
Please hear me out.
Would you kindly allow
me to borrow one Regalia?
I humbly beg of you.
Please!
[TENJIN] When corruption
has already set in.
There's no guarantee that using
Regalias can save a master.
What kind of Regalia
inflicts this much upon
its master in the first place?
[knuckles crack]
[TENJIN] You must
slay Yukine, Yato.
[phone ringing]
[KOFUKU]
Daikoku!
Yeah okay...
what?
[KOFUKU] You could
only find one Regalia?
What are we gonna
do, Daikoku?
[DAIKOKU]
Keep looking.
That's the only thing I can do.
[DAIKOKU]
Yeah. I-I know.
Mm, right.
I'll call you back later
with an update.
The only other gods
around here are...
[DAIKOKU gasps]
[KOFUKU whimpering]
We've gotta do something.
If we can't find someone else
to help us, Yatty's gonna die.
[KOFUKU sobs]
[HIYORI grunts]
[wind rushing]
[HIYORI]
Just one more!
I need to find one more Regalia.
[water drips]
[HIYORI]
There's always Nora.
I'm certain she'd
come to Yato's aid.
[HIYORI grunts]
Except, what would be the cost?
[NORA]
You know I'm good.
I can kill anything in your
way with no trouble.
[HIYORI]
She just might kill Yukine.
In that case.
[HIYORI panting]
[KAZUMA]
You should be more careful.
If you cross paths
with Bishamon again,
keep your head down, or things
could go badly for you.
[HIYORI panting]
[HIYORI gulps]
[HIYORI]
This is no time to be afraid.
Come out, Kazuma!
I need your help!
Please, Kazuma!
[KAZUMA] Has there been
activity in the northeast?
[KINUHA] It's all
fairly quiet.
There are no signs of any
vent openings for now.
[KAZUMA] And in
the southeast?
[TSUGUHA] All clear--
Nothing to report.
I'll continue to remain
alert though.
[HINAHA] I'm really
sorry, Kazuma, but well...
[KAZUMA]
Hm?
A girl's been
calling for you
outside a shrine
for a while now.
[BISHAMON]
What is it?
Well?
[KAZUMA]
Sorry it's nothing.
This girl's too ill-mannered
to even offer a bow.
Ignore her.
[HINAHA]
Okay.
Now then.
Let's get back
to your reports.
[HIYORI]
Please, Kazuma!
You have to talk to me!
Please, I need your help!
We're talking life
and death here, Kazuma!
Plea--
[KOFUKU] You couldn't
find one more person!
You dummy, what's
wrong with you?
You didn't even try
looking, did you?
[DAIKOKU] Of course
I looked!
But no one is willing
to take the risk to help
the Regalia of a god
they've never even heard of.
[MAYU] Please try
to hang in there.
[MAYU] We're trying.
[KOFUKU] What are we
[MAYU] Please, Yato!
[KOFUKU] gonna do now?
[YUKINE walking]
[DAIKOKU] Hey!
Didn't I tell
you not to move?
[YUKINE]
Do I look like I care?
[YUKINE grunts]
[KAZUMA] And where
are you going?
[DAIKOKU]
Kazuma?
[MAYU]
Who is that?
[KAZUMA] How's
Yato holding up?
[DAIKOKU ] Hold on, isn't Yato
your master's sworn enemy?
He is.
But I personally
owe him a debt.
On top of that.
[KAZUMA] She came
to me for help.
[KOFUKU]
Yori?
I suggest you give
her a stern lecture.
I've warned her myself, yet she
came right to our front door.
[KAZUMA] Veena would've
killed her if she had known.
[DAIKOKU]
Well,
I don't know what kind
of debt you owe him,
but we've got
our three Regalias now.
You do. But
the state he's in?
[ALL gasp]
This is not
going to be easy.
Yato.
Can you hear me?
You need
to banish Yukine.
You can't endure
this for much longer.
[YATO moaning]
Yato!
[MAYU] He just won't
listen to reason.
[DAIKOKU] That's why an ablution
is the only way we can save him.
[KAZUMA]
Yukine.
What'd you do?
I don't know.
Nothing.
[KAZUMA]
If that's true,
then why were you
just trying to leave?
[YUKINE]
'Cuz I wanted to, okay?
Or maybe it's because you
can't handle the guilt you feel.
[YUKINE] Or it's because I'm
sick and tired of all of you!
I said I didn't do
anything, alright?
[DAIKOKU]
Is that so?
Then you wouldn't mind taking
off your shirt for a sec.
[YUKINE]
Uh, what?
Why should I?
Just shut up
and do what I say.
[clothes rustling]
[PHANTOMS shriek]
[YUKINE gasps]
[HIYORI gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[PHANTOMS shrieking]
[YUKINE]
What is that?
[DAIKOKU]
Damn it!
You stung your master that much?
[DAIKOKU] Are you ready to do
this? [YUKINE] Nasty!
[MAYU] Yes.
[YUKINE] It's talking now!
[YUKINE] Hurry and get it off
me!
Please, just get it off!
[DAIKOKU]
We now cleanse this spirit
belonging to the god Yato,
and we preserve the name
with which it was graced.
[YUKINE]
What is this?
[KAZUMA] With defilement
expelled and avarice removed.
We bring forth a sincere,
principled, and just soul.
[MAYU] With flesh pared
may he be cleansed.
[ALL grunt]
[HIYORI gasps]
[YUKINE screaming]
[YATO screaming]
[HIYORI]
What're they-?
[KOFUKU]
An ablution involves
purifying the flesh
through burning.
They're using
the Regalia borderlines
to hold him in place
and cleanse him.
They're doing...
what?
They all used
to be human.
Only Regalias may judge
the sins of other Regalias.
[YUKINE]
Stop it!
Let me out, damn it!
And once an ablution
has officially begun,
it's not safe to stop
until it's over.
[KOFUKU]
Not until the Regalia
has confessed and repented
all of their sins.
Every last one of them.
Yukine!
Confess your evils!
Do it now!
Shut up!
I'll kill you for this!
[KOFUKU]
But if he refuses...
[HIYORI gasps]
[bones cracking]
[YUKINE moaning]
[YATO puking]
[KAZUMA]
Harder!
He's becoming a phantom!
[YUKINE screaming]
[PHANTOMS shrieking]
[YATO moaning]
[YUKINE screaming]
[KOFUKU]
Stop watching!
[HIYORI]
This is cruel!
You have
to stop them!
He can't take it!
[YUKINE gasping]
I didn't do anything
to deserve this!
Why the hell are you
putting me through this?
I didn't do anything wrong!
[PHANTOMS shrieking]
[YUKINE whimpering]
[YUKINE] All of this just
'cuz of some loose change?
[PHANTOMS shrieking]
So I stole some stuff,
and I broke some stuff!
Who freaking cares?
I didn't hurt anyone!
Don't act like you don't
understand me!
It's because we're dead!
[YUKINE]
But they're not!
They have everything!
And they don't even
appreciate it!
[BOY C] My folks are really
pissing me off.
[BOY E] I had my
brother help me.
[BOY F]
C'mon!
We're your friends!
[fence creaks]
[YUKINE] A future, memories,
a family and friends...
They get to have everything.
Everything that's
been taken from me.
They've got it all
and I have nothing!
It's not fair.
I'm completely alone.
And I have nothing.
Nothing at all.
[NORA] You have such
pretty eyes for a boy.
They remind me of the fruit
on hawthorn plants.
You know.
Not even birds will eat
the hawthorn fruit.
[YUKINE gasps]
[NORA] Not because
of their taste.
They aren't poisonous
or anything.
They're just empty is all.
Useless, empty fruit.
They offer nothing.
And of course nobody
bothers to pick them.
So they're left on the plant
to wilt, wither, and die.
[echoing]
and die...
[NORA giggling]
Poor, lonely little boy.
[YUKINE yelling]
[glass shattering]
[YUKINE sobbing]
[YUKINE yelling]
[glass shattering]
So what if I stole
a few things?
And why does it matter
if I smashed up some stuff?
Everyone should be like me.
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM] They should
be like me and die!
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM moans]
[swing creaking]
[YATO coughing]
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM shrieking]
It's just no use!
He's fighting too much!
Daikoku!
Change into the Kokki
and slay him!
[DAIKOKU] Keep your cool,
you mousy dumbass!
It'll collapse
if I transform now!
And besides.
I'd just open up a vent
in my Kokki form.
Now quit freakin' out
and try to think clearly!
[swing creaking]
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM growling]
[MAYU]
Look!
[KAZUMA] If his mark gets
enveloped, we're screwed!
[DAIKOKU]
Don't you give up now!
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM shrieking]
[YATO]
His name.
I need to say it.
I need to call his name.
Before it disappears.
When I picked him,
I had a feeling
he was more than a pretty face.
Isn't that right, Yukine?
[footsteps scuffing]
[YATO] I can't let him
cross to the other side.
I need to call his name.
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM growling]
[footsteps scuffing]
[HIYORI]
Yukine!
[KOFUKU]
Yori, No!
[DAIKOKU]
Hey! Get away!
It's too dangerous!
Yukine!
Don't cross to the other side!
You can't let yourself
become a Phantom!
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM roaring]
[HIYORI shrieks]
[KOFUKU gasps]
[HIYORI]
Listen to me, Yukine!
Yato is still here for you!
I know you know
that's true!
I know you heard him!
[YATO] He's a stupid punk
with an attitude problem,
but I found him,
and I named him.
Sekki!
I will re-forge you!
[HIYORI]
That's what he said.
He cares about
you like a father!
[footsteps halt]
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM grunting]
[HIYORI]
Think about it.
Even when you kept on betraying
Yato and hurting him,
he just endured it!
But if you keep hurting someone
who's that good to you,
Then I--
can't be friends
with you anymore!
[YUKINE]
Friends...
You're my friend?
[HIYORI whimpering]
[YATO coughs]
[YATO]
Yukine!
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM grunts]
[YATO groans]
I know it's hard,
and it's not fair.
You can't be with
people anymore.
I'm sorry that you're
no longer like them.
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM grunts]
[YATO]
But, Yukine...
I granted you the name
of a person!
[YUKINE'S PHANTOM grunts]
[YATO]
So...
You can still live as a person!
You can live, Yukine!
[YUKINE]
Yato...
I'm so...
I'm so sorry.
[YUKINE sobbing]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
I kept on stinging Yato!
I stole money!
And Hiyori.
I...
[YUKINE]
...I tried to feel her up!
I stole the
skateboard, too.
And I smashed out
all the windows!
And I told so many lies!
I won't do it anymore!
I promise!
I'm really sorry for everything!
I'm sorry!
[YUKINE sobbing]
[birds chirping]
[KOFUKU] Okay! There's no
blight to be found!
[BOTH sigh] I thought
I was a dead man.
[KOFUKU]
But you are dead.
[DAIKOKU] Why does punishment
gotta be so exhausting?
[YATO] I wanna thank you guys
for helping out this dimwit.
I appreciate it.
I would hope you do.
[YATO]
You too, Hiyori.
I never thought it'd cause
you this much trouble.
Yukine.
Come here, buddy.
[YUKINE grunts]
I'm sorry!
Now you tell
her, too!
Hiyori.
I'm sorry!
[YATO] If she hadn't thought
to bring us here.
I'm sure I would've died
where I was.
Also, if she had chosen
Nora as one of the Regalias.
Well, the pain was so intense,
I might have been tempted
to use Nora to end it.
And of course, if she hadn't
stopped Yukine when she did--
If she... hadn't been
by my side.
[HIYORI whimpers]
[YATO]
She saved us.
[HIYORI whimpers]
[YATO] She made every
right move and saved us.
[HIYORI sobbing]
I'm so relieved!
I'm so glad you're both okay!
[HIYORI sobbing]
[YUKINE sobbing]
I'm so...
I'm so sorry.
[BOTH sobbing]
[YUKINE]
Thank you.
♪ [NORA] The stew has
now started to bubble. ♪
♪ Is it ready to eat? ♪
♪ I'll taste it
and see for myself. ♪
♪ Munch, munch, munch. ♪
I really thought the Phantoms
were gonna munch him up
for sure back there.
Well, now I know
that waking you up
was the right choice after all.
Rabo.
♪ [NORA] The stew has now
started to bubble. ♪
♪ Is it ready to eat? ♪
♪ I'll taste it
and see for myself. ♪
[RABO]
It is ready.
Yato.
Is he truly the former
god of calamity?
The Yato?
I suppose you'll just
have to find out for yourself.
[KAZUMA] On the next Noragami:
"Regarded with Hate."
[MAYU]
So, it's nice to meet you.
I'm Mayu.
[DAIKOKU]
Oh, yeah, my name.
I'm Daikoku.
[KAZUMA]
I'm Kazuma.
Sorry, but I've gotta go now.
[MAYU]
Same here.
[DAIKOKU]
Uh-- Sure.
Later.
[DAIKOKU] Man, those two
are surprisingly alike.