[water rushing]
[BISHAMON] From what I could
see, he was ailing badly.
I shouldn't have let
him go like that.
[water rushing]
[BISHAMON]
Kazuma.
[KAZUMA]
I am here.
[BISHAMON]
Come outside.
[blinds rolling]
[water rushing]
[BISHAMON]
Report.
[KAZUMA]
Yes.
Three days have passed
since the Vent was opened.
With the help of affiliated
and unaffiliated shrines,
we have erected a barrier
that has halted its growth.
However, the Phantoms
that have already come out
will need
to be dealt with.
[BISHAMON] Have you
located Yato yet?
My Lady, I...
[BISHAMON]
Well? Yes?
We're alone here.
Speak your mind.
You really shouldn't leave
your hair wet like this.
You'll catch cold.
[BISHAMON sighs]
As you wish.
What kind of battle
was that, Lady?
[BISHAMON gasps]
[KAZUMA] You acted
on a personal grudge,
without thinking
about others.
As a master it was completely
irresponsible, Veena.
[BISHAMON]
That's enough.
[water splashing]
[water dripping]
[BISHAMON] Dealing with
the fallout from the Vent
is our priority now.
It was my fault the
damn thing was opened.
I am duty-bound to
exterminate those Phantoms.
Prepare to go hunting.
Now that is the
lady I follow.
[BISHAMON]
Kuraha! Kinuha! Yugiha!
Akiha! Karuha!
Kazuha! Tsuguha!
Let's go!
[knocking]
[HIYORI]
Yukine?
Are you awake yet?
[plastic rustling]
I brought breakfast,
so I hope you're hungry!
[YATO]
Thanks, Hiyori.
Sounds great.
[HIYORI shrieking]
What the--?
What are you
doing here, Yato?
You weren't invited!
Where's Yukine?
[YATO]
Oh, he ran away.
He's probably over
at Tenjin's place.
[HIYORI] He ran away,
and you didn't stop him?
Why would I?
It's not like I need
him right now, anyway.
[HIYORI grunts]
[plastic rustling]
[chip crunches]
[footsteps tapping]
HIYORI panting]
[HIYORI shrieks]
[TENJIN] Ah, hello
there, dear.
[HIYORI]
Hi, Lord Tenjin!
[TENJIN] Whatever
is the matter?
Having school
troubles?
I'm sorry.
I'm looking
for Yukine.
Ah. I saw him.
He came by
this morning.
[YUKINE] I'd like to work
for you instead of Yato.
Can I do that?
[TENJIN]
Hm.
[MAYU] So, the new kid only
lasted a month, huh?
[AYU] That doesn't
seem like long.
How long were you
Lord Yato's Regalia?
[MAYU]
Three whole months.
[MIYU]
Wow!
I don't know how you did it!
[MOYU]
No way I'd be able to.
[NAYU] That sounds
impossible.
That's enough,
ladies.
It does seem early
to have decided
you no longer want
Lord Yato as your master.
Is there
a specific reason?
I can't stand the guy.
Isn't that enough?
He doesn't have
a shrine, he's broke,
he's obnoxious, he has
a screwed-up past.
And besides, he already
has a Regalia.
So, there you go.
Why should I waste time hanging
around with a guy like that?
[TENJIN]
Hm.
While I'm flattered
and delighted
you would ask for my help,
I fear it wouldn't be
appropriate for me to agree.
You wouldn't want me
to give you a name
right now, child.
Doing that would make
you a Nora, you see.
[HIYORI]
Nora.
Sorry, but what does
that mean, exactly?
Until now I thought it
was just someone's name.
How should
I explain?
Noras are embarrassing.
Private parts of a god's
life, you know.
Get it?
Private parts.
Huh?
[TENJIN giggling]
[TSUYU]
My lord.
Perhaps you should
restrain yourself.
[TENJIN] It's only a figure
of speech, Tsuyu.
I'm not trying to
scandalize the girl!
[TENJIN coughs]
What is a Nora?
A Nora is a Regalia
with many owners.
Not unlike a stray
cat, for comparison.
But those who choose
to go by many names
are seen as less reliable
and more likely to
betray their masters.
As such, they are looked
down upon, despised.
[HIYORI grunts]
Think of
it his way.
What if I offered
to become your godfather?
I'll give you a pretty
new name and everything.
It'll be fun.
I would make
a great godparent!
Huh?
[TENJIN] Now, what
would be a good name?
Yumi, maybe?
Or Tomo? Yuko?
Um, thanks
a lot, but no.
See?
It feels disrespectful,
even a bit wrong, doesn't it?
Yeah...
The kind of idea that people
instinctively recoil from.
And that's how
Noras are seen.
Why they are regarded
with such hate.
They're that bad?
[water drips]
Oh, yes.
Normally, a Regalia has but one
name and serves only one master.
[TENJIN] It is commonly accepted
that to serve a new master,
one must first be "unnamed"
by the previous master.
Just as
Mayu was.
[HIYORI] If they're so reviled,
why do Noras even exist?
For unsavory
tasks.
To put it another way, they're
generally used to perform jobs
you wouldn't give
to your own Regalias.
[HIYORI gasps]
[HIYORI] Um...
Lord Tenjin.
I wonder if you know a girl
Nora I met a little while ago.
About the same age
as Yukine, I think--
[MAYU]
Please, that's enough.
We don't like
to talk about Noras.
[TSUYU] The very mention of them
sends shivers down our spines.
[HIYORI]
Oh.
[TSUYU] Though my lord does
seem to speak freely of them.
[TENJIN chuckling]
No need to worry.
I've never made use of one
before, nor do I intend to.
I have no wish
to entangle myself
with such wretched
creatures as Noras.
[water dripping]
[YATO groans]
[water drips]
[water rushing]
[NORA] Don't forget that you
can always use me.
[YATO]
Nora.
I've never stopped watching
you in all this time,
and yet you never
call for me anymore.
I've been so lonely.
[water bubbling]
That new boy
is unstable.
You should just
get rid of him.
[water bubbling]
[clothes rustling]
It's not like you
don't have options.
I can be useful.
Much more useful than he can.
[clothes rustling]
[HIYORI]
I've looked all over.
Where is he?
[HIYORI gasps]
I smell someone,
but it isn't Yato.
[HIYORI gasps]
[HIYORI]
It's Bishamon!
[HIYORI whimpering]
[HIYORI gasps]
That confirms it.
You can see us.
[HIYORI] You're one
of Bishamon's people!
And you're that strange
living spirit.
The half-Phantom
from before.
Yato has many
odd acquaintances.
I don't know why
I'm surprised.
[HIYORI]
I'm going to die!
[HIYORI grunts]
[HIYORI panting]
Restraint.
[chains clanging]
[HIYORI gasps]
[HIYORI] I can't
move a single inch.
[KAZUMA]
Umbra.
[HIYORI whimpering]
[HIYORI gasps]
[lion roaring]
[HIYORI]
Okay. Okay.
Maybe a god will
come to my rescue.
Aaahh! Yep!
I'm totally dead!
[BISHAMON]
Progress?
Do you have a location
on the next Phantom?
[KAZUMA]
No.
[KURAHA] There aren't
any here, milady.
Or none that I can
smell, anyway.
Kuraha's correct.
We have pretty much cleared
out this entire area.
All that remains is the
south-southeast region.
Oh?
[HIYORI]
Wait a sec.
They don't even
realize I'm here?
[BISHAMON] It's a bit soon,
but let's try widening the area.
[KAZUMA]
Indeed.
I'll catch up with you once
I've conducted one final search.
[BISHAMON]
Very well, then.
I'm sorry, Kuraha.
I know your wounds
haven't healed yet.
[KURAHA]
Don't worry, milady.
This is nothing.
Look after her.
I'll follow soon.
[KURAHA roaring]
Right!
[HIYORI]
Interesting.
They're nothing like
Lord Tenjin or Kofuku.
They work as one big team.
I didn't know that was possible.
[KAZUMA] I wouldn't meddle
if I were you, Hiyori Iki.
It could
be dangerous.
[HIYORI gasps]
Hey!
How do you know
what my name is?
And, uh, what did
you just do to me?
It's a talent
of mine:
manipulating the
things around me.
It often comes in handy,
given my line of work.
Would you like
this back?
[HIYORI] Hey!
You have my wallet!
But when could
you have...?
[HIYORI grunts]
You should
be more careful.
If you cross paths with Bishamon
again, keep your head down,
or things could
go badly for you.
I still don't understand
why you helped me.
I was under the impression
you hated Yato.
[KAZUMA]
Make no mistake.
He is certainly
our enemy.
However...
I also owe him
a great deal.
Speaking of which,
is he doing alright?
[HIYORI]
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
He was blighted.
It looked
to be pretty severe.
It's that bad?
The blight's source
wasn't external.
It most likely came
from the inside.
Yato's Regalia.
"Sekki" in that
form, right?
It should be disposed
of as soon as possible.
[HIYORI gasps]
What do you mean?
There's nothing
to worry about!
Yukine's a good kid.
He used to be human!
Isn't killing Regalias
like killing people?
[KOFUKU]
It was a long time ago,
but Yatty did kill
a Regalia once.
He kills people,
too, sometimes.
[HIYORI gasps]
[KAZUMA] Something must
be done before it's too late.
If a Regalia
repeatedly does wrong.
Its master will
fall seriously ill.
[KAZUMA] If left untreated,
the pain will intensify.
The blight will spread
throughout the body,
growing ever worse.
[KAZUMA sighs]
Honestly.
Why is he even using
such a Regalia?
[HIYORI]
Huh?
You appear to be his
close companion.
Has he not mentioned
anything about it to you?
Uh, no,
he hasn't.
I know this may seem
an odd request.
But please look
after Yato.
I'd hate to lose
him like this.
Right.
I'll see what
I can do.
Yukine must
be dealt with.
If that doesn't
happen soon...
[wind blowing]
[speaking inaudible]
[YUKINE]
Damn it!
Stupid, useless
old geezer!
[YATO] Got
rejected, did ya?
[YATO chuckles]
Shut up!
Well?
What do you want?
We got a job.
You coming?
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO grunts]
Gotta skim
the soup.
You call this a job?
Are you kidding?
You suck
at being a god!
Try a temp
agency instead!
Quiet, you
whiney brat!
This is an honest job
for an honest client.
The shop would have
to close its doors
without late
night help like us!
[soup splashes]
[YATO]
Oww! Hot! Hot! Hot!
[YUKINE]
This sucks.
Seriously.
Why do I put up with
this kinda crap?
[doorbell chimes]
[DAIKOKU]
Oh, you're actually here.
[YATO]
And so are you.
[KOFUKU]
Hey there, Yatty!
No! Not her!
[KOFUKU shrieking]
[YATO]
No gods of poverty wanted here!
[DAIKOKU]
You punk!
Think I'll let you
touch my lady like that?!
[YATO yells]
[crashing sound]
It's justice and you know it!
You two go around
tricking people
with that fake name of hers.
It's just plain shady!
She uses a trade name!
Plenty of other places
do the same thing!
[BOTH growling]
Owie!
Rub my boo-boo, Yori.
It hurts!
There, poor thing.
Does that help?
[YATO]
Hiyori?
How's your latest gig?
[HIYORI sighs]
We love Yori.
She's been so helpful.
She brought us straight to you!
You brought them?
How'd you even know
where I was, though?
Um... actually,
it's your sm...
Same thing
when we asked.
She won't
cough it up.
"Cough it up"?
What are you,
a gangster?
[YATO]
Well? Whatcha doin' here?
[DAIKOKU] We got a job
that's not our style.
So we were gonna see
if you wanted it.
You do want it,
don't you?
I guess
I could take it.
Hey, uh, you're looking
a little pale.
How do you feel?
[YATO grunts]
[HIYORI gasps]
[DAIKOKU]
Aw, man.
Couldn't afford dinner again?
[HIYORI gasps]
[YATO]
Yukine.
What'd you do this time?
What?
[change rattling]
[YUKINE] You don't really think
I stole money, do you?
That's messed up.
Oh, come on, man.
Even a god's given up on me.
Great.
[YUKINE] I was better off
being dead than working for you.
[YUKINE panting]
[change rattling]
[DAIKOKU]
So Yato was right.
You did steal it.
[YUKINE panting]
[KOFUKU]
Oh dear. That's bad.
[clothes rustling]
I'll take that
job, thanks.
You guys'll stay and look
after the shop, right?
[DAIKOKU]
Huh?
Wait! Get back here!
[KOFUKU]
That'll be 582 yen, please!
Thanks fer your business, sir.
[MAN shrieking]
[YATO] All
it says is to
"eliminate the Phantom that
has appeared above Kamiido."
That's a simple
enough job.
Yeah.
I'll bet branch shrines
are getting lots of these
types of requests since
the Vent was opened.
[HIYORI]
Yato.
About Yukine--
[YATO]
I'll find him.
Can't do much Phantom
slaying without a Regalia.
That's why you really gotta keep
track of the things, you know?
No. I wasn't asking--
I mean,
what I wanted--
How do I
say this?
[YATO] I know.
I get it.
This problem needs
to be put to rest.
[HIYORI gasps]
[KAZUMA] It should be disposed
of as soon as possible.
[HIYORI grunts]
[HIYORI sniffling]
[slap]
Huh?
[HIYORI slapping]
Whoa!
You've finally lost it,
haven't you?
[HIYORI sighs]
Uh...
[YATO gasps]
[HIYORI]
Yato.
Uh, yeah?
Regalias
aren't tools.
"Gotta keep track
of the things"?
[YATO]
Huh?
Yukine isn't
some thing.
You have to treat
him like a person.
If you're not
willing to do that,
how can you expect
him to act like one?
Think about it, okay?
Sure. I will.
[water drips]
[YUKINE gasping]
[NORA] You have such
pretty eyes for a boy.
They remind me of the fruit
on hawthorn plants.
You know.
Not even birds will eat
the hawthorn fruit.
[YUKINE gasps]
[NORA]
Not because of their taste.
They aren't
poisonous or anything.
They're just empty, is all.
Useless, empty fruit.
They offer nothing.
And of course nobody
bothers to pick them.
So they're left on the plant
to wilt, wither, and die
as pointlessly
as they lived.
[NORA giggles]
Poor, lonely little boy.
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO]
Yukine!
[YATO] What are you
doing with him, Nora?
[NORA]
You know, Yato.
You should really use me more.
Like you used to.
[HIYORI gasps]
[NORA]
You know I'm good.
I can kill anything
in your way with no trouble.
[NORA]
Come on.
Sekki!
[YUKINE grunts]
[YATO] Don't listen
to anything Nora says.
She's vindictive.
Focus on one thing.
On that.
Now? Are you sure?
[YATO grunts]
[HIYORI]
Wait! Yato!
[YATO grunts]
[YATO panting]
This is the land
of the rising sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me.
I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee
waste with the Sekki
and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
[PHANTOM groans]
He can't cut through it?
[PHANTOM groaning]
[YATO panting]
You've gotta be
kidding with this!
He's already gotten dull?
All the stings I've
gotten 'cause of him.
Now there's this?
[PHANTOM]
Smells nice.
Hurry! Get out of there!
[YATO groaning]
[PHANTOM] Smells nice,
nice, nice, nice.
[water splashes]
[PHANTOM moans]
[YATO groaning]
[PHANTOM groaning]
[YATO panting]
Purification water.
Go, Nora!
Just get out of here!
[YATO] He's a stupid punk
with an attitude problem,
but I found him,
and I named him.
Sekki!
I will re-forge you!
Rend!
[PHANTOM groaning]
[twinkling]
[HIYORI sighs]
They did it!
[RABO]
Rejected you, huh?
So much for his reputation.
He's not the god he used to be.
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO]
Let's go.
[traffic wooshing]
[footsteps scuffing]
[KAZUMA]
Yukine must be dealt with.
If that doesn't
happen very soon.
Then Yato
will die.
[door snaps]
At this rate, he'll die.
[DAIKOKU] Sorry for decking
you like that earlier, man.
[YATO]
Don't worry about it.
[DAIKOKU]
Here.
To show there's
no hard feelings.
Take it.
[YATO]
Daikoku.
[DAIKOKU] Next time on
Noragami: "Over the Line."
[YATO]
Hey, hold on!
This looks like a medical bill!
[DAIKOKU] My lady's got a lump
on her head 'cause of you!