[YUKINE panting]
[DAIKOKU]
Yukine.
[DAIKOKU] Tend to the shop
once you're done in there.
[YUKINE]
'Kay!
[patting fabric]
[liquid flowing]
[slurping]
[YUKINE]
Nice.
The oden's
ready now.
[DAIKOKU]
Great.
Glad to see you're off
to such a good start.
[HIYORI]
Hey!
Good morning, you two.
[YUKINE]
Hey!
Good to see you!
[HIYORI] So you really did pick
up a part-time job here, huh?
[YUKINE]
Well, it's just.
I need to.
I wanna pay back the
money I took, y'know?
Aw, Yukine.
[DAIKOKU] I may be
made out of stone,
but even I coundn't say
no when he told me that.
You were on the
wrong path,
but it looks like you've finally
staightened yourself out.
Uh.
Yeah, that is
part of it.
But it's also because
Yato doesn't ever
make any damn money!
[YATO shrieking]
[DAIKOKU]
Oh, yeah.
Don't you have a favor you were
gonna ask Hiyori?
I said that wasn't
a big deal!
What is it?
Um, well, uh.
[DAIKOKU] You're getting set to
move onto a new grade, right?
He was hoping you
wouldn't mind passing
your old textbooks on to him if
you still have them around.
[DAIKOKU] He wants to start
acting like a normal kid again.
It's cool if you
don't want to-
[HIYORI sobbing]
Of course
I don't mind!
You can have
them all!
Huh?
[BOTH sobbing]
[YUKINE] What is wrong with
you guys lately?
[KOFUKU]
Oh, there you are!
[KOFUKU] I've been
looking for you two.
[KOFUKU] Just so
you don't forget.
You owe me
money, too.
[YATO stuttering]
[HIYORI gasping]
[KOFUKU]
Oh, c'mon, Yori.
Don't tell me you
already forgot
that you asked us
to save Yatty for you.
Cuz we did the work.
And this is how
much we charge.
[HIYORI]
Five yen?
I can do that.
5 million, and we
did help you twice.
Ten million?
[KOFUKU] Oh, don't
you worry.
A girl as cute and smart
and capable as you are,
I'm sure you can earn that
amount it in no time at all.
[YATO]
Wait, Kofuku.
Hiyori's still
in school.
What about the
student discount?
Oh, good point.
So.
We'll call it
one million.
[YATO]
Good deal!
90 percent off!
That is one
serious bargain!
[YATO] And this is why
it pays to do business
[YATO]
with the god of poverty.
[HIYORI] You still haven't
even fixed my body yet!
And now you've
put me in debt?
[HIYORI]You will
help me pay this off!
[DAIKOKU] Man, what fighting
federation does she belong to?
[YATO]
Tenjin!
I wanted to drop by and say
thanks for your help!
[TENJIN] I heard you
really let yourself
get put through
the ringer.
Yeah, I guess so.
[MAYU]
What, you guess so?
How could you ever let your
blight get that out of control?
Your Regalia had you
on the verge of death.
[YATO] Well, the Sekki
has incredible potential.
I couldn't just throw away
his talent like that.
And besides that, I wanted
to reforge him properly.
I intentionally let
my condition get that bad.
just to give him
a stern wake-up call.
[TENJIN]
Well.
I suppose I understand
your method.
Yeah,
but regardless.
You guys really saved
my butt, especially you, Tomone.
I guess we're
still friends.
That's Mayu for you.
She is a gutsy,
dependable girl.
All thanks to a certain
lowlife who took her in.
Well, I am one
hell of a teacher.
Oh, yes, and your method
follows the four Cs, I believe.
[TENJIN] Crass.
[HIYORI] Are they friends now?
[TENJIN] Childish.
[TENJIN] Crude.
[YUKINE] I can't tell.
[TENJIN] And Clueless.
[MAYU] Come, come.
[YATO] No!
[MAYU] Why don't we
[YATO] Cool, classy,
[MAYU] talk somewhere else?
[YATO] confident, and cultured!
[HIYORI]
Hey.
Aren't you missing
one of the Regalias?
I think her name was Miyu?
[MAYU]
Unfortunately.
She was kicked out
for stinging Lord Michizane.
[YUKINE]
She was corrupted?
[MAYU]
You see.
What happened
to you, Yukine,
is actually
very contagious.
Just seeing or hearing
about it can affect others.
[liquid splatters]
[MAYU] A single sting to a
master results in banishment.
[MAYU] Lord Michazane
has never once made an exception
[MAYU] to this rule.
[MIYU] I'm sorry!
[MAYU] To harm others
or yourself, [MIYU] I'm sorry!
[MAYU] whether intenional
or not,
is to betray the
master who named you.
Banishment is actually
seen as an act of generosity
after an ablution.
Because a new master
might take you in.
If you're lucky that is.
Otherwise.
[YUKINE]
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
It simply
couldn't be helped.
But please.
You mustn't let
this bother you,
no matter how upsetting
it may be.
It might have an effect
on Yato.
Believe me when
I tell you this, Yukine.
We understand
how you felt.
[MAYU] Regalias are
easily corrupted
if they don't maintain
their borderlines.
Ultimately, we're still
Far Shore beings
who dwell alongside
Phantoms.
You must be careful.
The darkness
is always with you.
[YUKINE]
The darkness.
[MAYU] Despite everything,
Yato refused to banish you.
And now
it's your turn.
Swear on your name.
to always protect him.
[YUKINE]
Of course.
I swear on my
name: Yuki.
[HIYORI giggling]
What's funny?
[YATO ]
By the way, Tenjin.
I could use some advice
if you've got it to give.
[TENJIN]
Hmm?
It actually has to do
with Hiyori.
Ya see, after
her accident, she kinda
slips in and out
of her spirit form.
[TENJIN]
Oh.
[YATO] The thing is, I accepted
her request to fix it;
which would be fine.
If I knew what
in the hell to do!
But I've just
kept on putting it off.
I've gotta do it,
though.
She's helped me out several
times now, so it's only right!
Now's the time to finally
tackle her job!
[TENJIN] It's remarkable how
much of a lost cause you are.
Have you considered maybe
cutting her ties with you?
Huh?
[TENJIN] It's just a guess,
but doing so might
actually fix
her condition.
[YATO]
Wait, cut her ties?
[TENJIN] It seems to me that
the connection between you
grants her too much
of a focus on our world.
Try cutting that connection
as a test.
Shouldn't be hard
for you.
[AMI] Studying at the library's
so much better
than studying
at home.
[HIYORI]
No kidding.
[YAMA] Another day
of solid studying!
I'm feeling good!
[AMI] It can only do so much
with the exams we've got coming.
We really need to pick
a shrine to pray at.
Yeah!
We've gotta
pray to a god!
I wish to graduate
and be popular and be healthy
and be popular
and for my family to be safe!
You wished
to be popular twice.
Well, it's that
important.
[HIYORI giggling] That
sure is a lot of wishes.
Don't burden
the gods.
Isn't it pretty much
the gods' job
to hear people's
wishes, though?
I mean, why should I care
about their schedules?
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Speaking of wishes.
There's one god people
have been talking about lately.
Oh, yeah, I know.
Wait, which god?
They say that if you
tell him the name
of someone you
want gone,
he'll actually make them
disappear for you.
"Lord Rabo,
Lord Rabo.
I humbly beg of you!"
That's it, right?
[AMI]
That's how it goes.
His name's Rabo?
[HIYORI] That's the first I've
ever heard of that god.
[YAMA]
It's just a dumb fad.
[AMI]
Exactly.
What's with the school
books, Hiyori?
Yeah, those
are our old ones.
What are you luggin'
those around for?
I'm giving them
to a friend of mine.
[DAIKOKU]
What's up, kids!
You workin' hard in here?
[YATO]
Daikoku!
I'll take one of
those snacks!
[DAIKOKU] What the hell
are you doing in our home?
[YATO]
Oh, c'mon, man.
Don't be so cold.
[DAIKOKU] This room
is for Yukine!
Not your lazy ass!
Go suck on some tea leaves
if you're hungry!
[DAIKOKU] Jeez.
[YATO groaning]
[HIYORI]
It's still not right.
Do it again.
[YUKINE]
Hiyori.
You're kind of strict.
[HIYORI] It's easy to mess up
this part and this part.
Try to stay
focused.
Okay.
[YATO]
Hold on!
Let me see.
The real trick
to learning.
You've gotta
draw the stuff!
[YATO]
There!
The Pillow Book's
Sei Shonagon.
Hojoki's Kamo-no-Chomei.
and Tsurezuregusa's
Yoshida Kenko.
[BOTH]
You're good!
I know,
it's impressive.
It took work.
But with as long as I've
been a god, it ju--
[YUKINE]
Don't ruin my stuff!
I didn't ruin it!
I graced it
with my talent!
Why don't you
use that talent
to earn some money
for a change!
[YUKINE] Why have you always
gotta butt in, huh?
[YATO] What's
that supposed to mean?
[HIYORI]
What's wrong?
Uh. Nothing.
Don't worry about it.
[HIYORI'S MOM] Hiyori!
Could you add the black beans
[HIYORI'S MOM] to these for me?
[HIYORI] Okay!
[FEMALE NEWS BROADCASTER]
The person responsible for
the street slashings yesterday
morning has yet to be found.
Despite having taken place in
plain sight of others, no --
[HIYORI'S MOM] There've been a
lot of stories
about this slasher on the news
lately.
I know it's New Year's but--
I wish you'd stay home tonight.
[HIYORI]
It's just a shrine visit.
And I'll have
Yama and Ami with me.
[HIYORI'S MOM]
I still can't help but worry.
[phone chimes]
[HIYORI giggles]
[dog panting]
[YUKINE groans]
[YUKINE] I can't believe
you took a dumb job like this
on New Year's Eve
of all nights.
[YATO] Hey, you gotta take
the work when the work comes.
And end-of-year cleaning
can be pretty lucrative.
But I've gotta ask.
Does a dog really need
its own mansion?
[YUKINE]
I know, it's huge!
Right?
No way!
It's even got
a heated floor!
Are you serious?
I am so freakin' jealous!
[phone rings]
Hello!
You have successfully
reached Delivery God Yato.
Available
365 days a year.
[HIYORI]
Yato.
[YATO]
Oh, Hiyori!
Hey, what's
going on with ya?
[YUKINE]
Hm?
[HIYORI]
Well uh.
Do you wanna come
to the Tenjin shrine tonight
for the first visit
of the new year?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[YATO] Why d'you wanna
visit that geezer?
You can't think of another
god to visit tonight?
I'm kind of insulted.
[HIYORI] Well, I've got
my exams coming up.
[YUKINE] And you don't even
have a shrine to visit.
[YATO grunts]
Guess I'll have to use
your wages to buy one!
Are you a god
or a pimp?
[HIYORI laughing]
[HIYORI] You don't
have to visit the shrine.
There'll be food stalls
there too.
Food stalls?
We're in!
[YATO] Oh, man, I want
some candied fruit!
[HIYORI]
I'll see you guys soon.
[HIYORI giggles]
[phone pinging]
All-out, huh?
Hmmm.
[rope stretching]
[gong ringing]
[HIYORI'S MOM] Now make sure
you don't run in this.
You don't want it to come
loose and fall off of you.
[HIYORI]
I know.
Let's see you.
Oh, you look
lovely.
Well, I better go.
[high-pitched ringing]
[HIYORI gasps]
[HIYORI]
Huh.
[RABO] So that's
the half-Phantom deluding Yato.
[NORA]
That's her.
[RABO]
Let's slay her.
Reiki.
Not yet.
[RABO]
And why not?
It would
be wasteful.
She can still
be of use to us.
[traffic moving]
[AMI]
Hiyori!
[YAMA] You got all
dressed up for new year.
[HIYORI]
Yeah!
You said
"all out"!
We are going
all out!
I'm offering a ton
of money this year!
We've got the test and a new
school to worry about,
and popularity!
[AMI]
Simmer down, dummy.
[AMI] I think it's pretty
safe to say
the whole class will
move on to the next grade.
[YAMA] Hiyori's playin'
it safe with that outfit.
That's not why
I'm wearing it!
So...
I uh...
I wanted to let
you guys know
that someone might
join us later.
If that's cool.
[YAMA shrieking]
What?
Is it a guy?
Is that why
you're dressed up?
[AMI]
Hm!
So you're scheming
to win his heart
by convincing him you're
a different person this year?
[HIYORI]
Huh, no!
I swear
it's not like that!
[YAMA] You've got some serious
ambition for the new year.
Full blast
out of the gate.
[HIYORI] Honestly, I'm telling
you, it's not like that!
Jeez!
Just drop it already!
[crowd murmuring]
[coins clattering]
[YAMA] Popularity, popularity,
popularity, popularity,
please gimme popularity, please,
please, please, I just wanna be
[YAMA] popular!
[HIYORI] Please let me move onto
[YAMA] Popularity, popularity!
[HIYORI] the next grade
[HIYORI]
without trouble.
I used to visit shrines
just 'cuz I was supposed to,
but now, please let me continue
to have fun
with all my new friends.
[AMI] I want some octopus
dumplings.
[YAMA]
They look tasty!
[AMI]
Hey, Hiyori.
You gonna buy some?
[HIYORI]
Oh--
Mm-hm.
[HIYORI]
Yato!
Wait up!
[YAMA]
Hm?
Hiyori!
Hey, Hiyori!
Wake up!
[AMI] Her first narcoleptic
fit of the year.
Aw, man.
[YUKINE] I can't believe we
missed ringing in the new year
just to clean
a dog mansion.
[YATO] You
have no work ethic!
If I get hired to clean, I'm not
leaving until the job is done!
I just hope Hiyori
hasn't gotten sick of waiting.
[phone rings]
[YUKINE]
A text?
[YATO] Yeah, it's for another
Phantom-slaying job.
Hey, wait, according
to the message.
It says to show up
right around here.
[phantom growling]
[BOTH gasp]
[YATO]
Come! Sekki!
[chime rings]
[YATO yelling]
[phantom growling]
[sword slashes]
[YATO grunts]
[sword slashing]
[phantom groaning]
[chime rings]
[YATO] This is the land
of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me.
I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki.
And expel thy
vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
[YATO grunts]
[phantom groaning]
[twinkling]
[YATO]
Alright.
Nicely done, kid.
[YUKINE]
Hey, thanks.
[sword swishing]
[YATO grunts]
[YATO gasps]
[YUKINE]
Huh?
We've gotta fight that many?
[YATO]
Stay calm, Yukine.
We've got this.
[phantoms clammoring]
[YATO] Listen to me.
You've really grown a lot,
and you're only gonna keep
growing stronger.
You've gotta believe
in yourself!
[YUKINE gasps]
[chime rings]
[phantoms clammoring]
[RABO]
Let me see, Yato.
Show me the power
of this Regalia.
Display his true worth to you.
[HIYORI]
Yato?
Are you here?
[HIYORI sniffing]
[HIYORI thinking]
I'm not picking up
his scent around here.
[water drips]
[chimes ringing]
[HIYORI]
Nora.
Um.
Hi, Nora.
Hey, have you
seen Yato?
I thought I saw him
come this way, but...
[clothes rustling]
What's that?
[NORA] I would appreciate it
[HIYORI] Is it-
[NORA] if you wouldn't speak to
me in such a casual manner,
you lowly Phantom.
Huh?
[HIYORI shrieks]
Whoa,
when did I?
The ablution.
I know you played
a large part in the ritual.
You were watching?
That was the perfect
chance to revoke his name.
And you
squandered it.
Huh?
[dogs growling]
[HIYORI yelps]
[HIYORI shrieks]
[dogs snarling]
[NORA giggles]
[NORA] You're quite fast
on your feet, I see.
Go after her Cord.
But please try
not to accidentally bite it off.
[dogs snarling]
[HIYORI shrieking]
[dog whimpering]
[dogs snarling]
[HIYORI grunting]
[HIYORI] Why are you
attacking me?
[NORA]
You want to know why?
Frankly, because
I don't like you.
[YUKINE] It's like there's
no end to these things!
[YATO] Yeah, they're persistent
to say the least!
[phantom growling]
[phantom groaning]
[HIYORI panting]
[dogs snarling]
[dogs growling]
[HIYORI panting]
[dogs whimpering]
[masks clatter]
[HIYORI]
They vanished.
[HIYORI groans]
[HIYORI sighs]
[NORA]
How disappointing.
I suppose that's it
for my masked ones.
Were you afraid?
Something even more
frightening is about to happen.
Huh?
A god of calamity
known as Rabo has awoken.
Rabo?
[YAMA]
"Lord Rabo, Lord Rabo.
I humbly beg of you!"
[HIYORI]
What about him?
[NORA] If someone
wishes for it,
Rabo can easily dispatch
the life of a Phantom.
Or the life
of a person.
of a god.
A blood-soaked,
aberrant god of calamity
from the Far Shore--
Rabo has come,
and he intends to kill Yato.
[HIYORI gasps]
No...
But...
...But Yato has
Yukine with him.
[NORA] Yato has grown weak
from his time spent with you.
If you care
about Yato.
Then please.
Stop existing.
[YATO grunts]
[YATO]
C'mon, come get me!
[YATO grunting]
[sword slashing]
[YUKINE]
Alright.
You've got 'em all rounded up.
[YATO]
That's right.
Now show me the power
of your ragged heart.
Let your rage out.
The same rage that drove you
to break those school windows
and hurt all you touched!
[YUKINE]
Fine! Okay!
Shut up!
[YATO] Harness that rage
and we'll take 'em out!
[chime rings]
This is the land
of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me.
I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki.
And expel thy
vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
[sword slashing]
[phantoms exploding]
[twinkling]
[YATO sighs]
[phantom grunts]
[phantom groans]
[twinkling]
[YATO] And that's all
there is to it.
Well done.
[YATO]
Now let's go find Hiyori!
[YUKINE]
Yeah!
I can't wait!
[YATO singing]
Candied fruit!
I'm gonna buy candied fruit
with Hiyori's money-- what the?
[YUKINE] Don't you
owe her enough?
[phantoms whining]
[jar shattering]
[RABO]
That's it?
That's Yato's strength now?
That's what he's become?
[YAMA] Please don't pass out
while walking home, alright?
[HIYORI giggling]
I'll be okay.
[YATO]
Hiyori!
[YUKINE] Hey, happy new year,
sorry we're so late.
[YATO]
Happy New Year!
Whoa, hold on.
You're not goin' home,
are ya?
C'mon, the food stalls
are still open, let's go!
It'll be the first
food offering of the year!
Unless.
You'd rather make
your first money offering.
[HIYORI]
Uh...
Huh?
I um.
Somethin' wrong,
Hiyori?
Do we know
each other?
Who are you?
[cars driving]
[KAZUMA] What's wrong, Veena?
Have you caught a cold-
[KAZUMA sneezes]
[BISHAMON]
Actually, it looks like
I'm not the only one sneezing
here, Kazuma.
[KAZUMA] Next time on Noragami:
"Abandoned God"
Huh? Are these hairballs?
[BISHAMON] Oh, Kuraha must
be shedding.