[wind rushing]
[metalic gliding]
[drums and horns sounding]
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[metal clanging]
[sword slashing]
[MEN grunting]
[metal clanging]
[MEN shouting]
[drum beat slowing]
[water rushing]
[drum slowly thrumming]
[MAN sheathing sword]
[drum fading]
[water rushing]
[NORA]
Rabo.
[MAN whimpers]
[RABO] Reiki.
[chimes ringing]
[MAN whimpers]
[RABO  grunting]
[sword slashing]
[metalic chime]
[YATO wailing] What the hell
is going on here?
[KOFUKU muffled]
Sounds like Yatty and Yukki
have finally made
their way home.
[DAIKOKU] Yeah, when
exactly did those two
become a part
of our household?
[YATO shouting] This doesn't
make sense, what's happening?
[YUKINE]Think you
could try to calm down?
Seriously.
Calm down?
But what's wrong
with Hiyori?
[HIYORI]
Uh, Yukine.
This guy you're with...
Who is he?
[YUKINE]
What do you mean?
[YATO laughing] Nice one,
Hiyori, now quit jokin' around.
C'mon, it's me,
ya dummy!
Meyadummy.
That's your name?
Yeah!
[YATO in Italian accent]
Mister Meyadummy!
That's'a me!
Well that was
a stupid accent!
[YATO laughing]
So, Yukine?
He's a friend
of yours?
Is he a comedian
or something?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[YUKINE] It's gotta be
some form of amnesia.
[YATO wailing]
It must be!
The really weird
thing about it is that
the only thing she seems
to have forgotten is you.
[YATO wailing]
What do we do?
For starters,
quit freaking out.
I bet it's just
a temporary condition.
I'm sure she'll
remember you soon.
[YATO]
No.
No what?
I will make Hiyori
normal again.
[YATO blowing whistle]
[YATO]
That's it!
Follow me this way!
[HIYORI] I was actually
just dropping by
to give you these
old reference books to study.
[YUKINE] I know, but just
humor him, will ya?
If I can direct your
attention to the left.
This street!
This famous street.
This is the very location
where the god Yato
met a certain girl
while rescuing Milord!
[ALL] Huh?
[HIYORI] A lord used to
live around here?
That's cool.
I had no idea there was
so much history to this street.
[YATO and YUKINE
exasperated sighing]
[YUKINE] I don't think that's
jogging her memory.
[YATO growling]
Do you know his name,
Mr. Yato?
The lord.
"Mr. Yato"?
It's Yato!
There's no "mister"!
You only call me
Yato!
[HIYORI]
Okay.
It just seems kind of rude
to call you that right away.
[YATO frustrated grunting]
I'll show you,
Hiyori!
Hey!
Quit drawing
in my books!
[YATO]
This is Milord!
He's a cat!
Oh, wow.
That's great!
You're talented,
Mr. Yato.
[YATO] I'm trying to show you
the drawing, not my artistry!
Oh, that's right.
Milord was the name
of the cat that you drew.
You remember
the cat?
So, do you
remember me then?
Let me think.
You're a
manga artist?
[YATO groans]
I'm sorry, but
I really need to get going.
[HIYORI]
Do you mind if we
do your lessons
another time, Yukine?
I've put your homework
assignments in here
until we can meet.
[YUKINE]
Sure.
Thanks.
See ya.
Wait!
Please, Hiyori.
Do you really not
remember me?
Just try to think.
Is there
nothing there?
In that case...
[HIYORI gasps]
[YATO whispering] Let's get
into bed together.
That just might help
you remember when
we met at
the hospital--
[HIYORI shouting]
Pervert!
[YATO wailing]
[KOFUKU] Yatty and Yukki
wanted us
to put some dinner aside
for them to eat later.
[DAIKOKU] Right.
Meals are the one thing
they never seem to miss.
[YUKINE] A picture book
of her memories?
After everything else,
you really think
that's gonna work?
[YATO]
Yes!
It will!
You saw how she
reacted earlier!
The drawing of Milord clearly
woke something inside her!
Now quit naysaying and
help me here!
Whatever.
You can make your own
coloring book.
[water splashing]
[HIYORI sighing]
[HIYORI thinking]
It's weird.
That guy seemed so desperate.
I wonder why it's
so important to him.
[HIYROI sighing]
[water dripping]
[YATO] Alright!
I've got all the tools
for a vivid picture book!
It won't be long now!
[YUKINE] Man, I can't believe
you threw away
what little money you had
on some stupid art supplies.
Anything for the
sake of Hiyori!
Now that I
think about it.
Maybe something specific
caused this.
[water dripping]
Yato?
What's wrong?
[chimes ringing]
[YUKINE gasps]
I should have known
you were somehow
behind this. Nora.
[YUKINE gasps]
[NORA] Behind what, Yato?
Erasing Hiyori's
memories of you?
It was actually
rather easy.
There's no reason for her
to retain memories
of Far Shore denizens
in her simple mind.
It seems that people are
quick to forget
that they've ever met you.
Wouldn't you agree?
No matter how much
you grant humans' wishes,
their behavior is always
so fickle and erratic.
Poor Yato, don't you ever
get tired of being hurt so much?
Why keep putting
yourself through it?
Wouldn't it be easier to
simply embrace your true self?
Yato!
Snap out of it!
Don't let her
mess with your head!
You're right.
Fine, Nora
just what the hell
are you scheming
this time?
[NORA giggles]
I only wanted
to get your attention
to make sure that you
haven't forgotten us, Yato.
[YATO gasping]
[RABO]
Reiki.
[chimes ringing]
[BOTH gasp]
You.
It can't be.
[YATO]
Rabo!
How are
you alive?
[RABO] It's been a
long time, Yato god.
[YUKINE]
Who is he?
That's a cute sun visor
you're wearing.
[chimes ringing]
Let's begin.
[wind rushing]
[YATO shouting]
Come. Sekki!
[markers clattering]
[swords clanging]
[swords slashing]
[YATO grunting]
[YUKINE] Whoa!
You actually wanna
kill this guy?
[YATO] If I hold back
even a little bit
he'll kill me right away.
[water bubbling]
[water rushing]
[YATO grunting]
[YUKINE grunting]
[YATO panting]
[YATO grunting]
[leaves rustling]
[sword slashing]
[RABO smirking]
[water bubbling]
[YATO]
Damn!
He's as fast as always!
[swords clanging]
[swords rattling]
[YATO groaning]
[RABO]
Yato god.
What has become of you?
[RABO] This is not the power
of the god I once knew.
You must remember.
[YATO gasps]
[RABO]
You must remember.
You must remember...
[RABO shouting]
You must remember!
[YUKINE shouting]
Yato!
[sword grinding]
[YUKINE]
Yato, are you okay?
Yato!
[chimes ringing]
[KAZUMA]
As for the next report--
[BISHAMON]
What is this?
[suspenseful music]
[TENJIN]
What's happening?
[swords clanging]
[YATO shouting]
[YUKINE groaning]
Yato.
[YATO]
Yukine!
[sword scraping]
[RABO]
There's no doubt.
The Yato god I knew
is a thing of the past.
Furuhime.
[chimes ringing]
[NORA]
I know, but now you see.
Listen, Yato.
[thunder and wind rushing]
I'd like to see you defeat Rabo.
If you do.
[NORA] I'll return
Hiyori Iki's memory to her.
[YATO and YUKINE gasping]
[NORA] And that's a promise.
[NORA laughing]
[wind rushing]
[KAZUMA] So, as far as this
sudden storm goes?
[DAIKOKU]
Nope.
[DAIKOKU] I'm afraid my lady's
got nothin' to do with it.
You're the first
god I come to
when a Vent
randomly opens.
I never would've thought
Yato was involved.
[YUKINE]
It was brutal.
We couldn't even come close
to taking down this Rabo guy.
[KOFUKU]
Rabo, huh?
[DAIKOKU] I've never
heard of the dude.
A god of calamity.
Nobody has spoken
his name in ages now.
[KAZUMA] But he was apparently
well-known long ago.
[MAYU] Then you
know him, master?
[TENJIN] Rabo was in fact
originally human.
As I recall, in his life,
he served as a Herald.
What's a Herald?
A minion who
sneaks into enemy land.
A thug who carries out
dirty work.
[TENJIN] Once a Herald
finishes his work,
his master kills him
to ensure his silence.
Seriously?
[KAZUMA]
Apparently.
He was deified
after he was murdered,
and turned into
a god of calamity.
[YUKINE] Wait, what's a
god of calamity?
People don't always ask
the gods for good things.
There are bad wishes.
[YUKINE]
Really?
Like what?
The destruction of someone
you hate, for example.
A god of calamity hears
these wicked requests.
[KAZUMA]
and fulfills them.
[TENJIN] Rabo favored
senseless murder
[TENJIN] as his particular
method in granting these wishes.
[TENJIN] There's no
discernment to his actions.
[TENJIN]
He kills Phantoms.
He kills humans.
[KAZUMA] And he's even
been known to kill gods.
[KAZUMA]
On request.
[YUKINE]
Wha--?
[YUKINE] What does someone
like that want with Hiyori?
[DAIKOKU] I'm guessing
he's an old pal of Yato's?
I have heard
certain rumors.
[KAZUMA] Yato did allegedly
partner with a god of calamity.
[YATO] Rabo hasn't
changed at all.
He's just as powerful.
If I'm not careful,
he might kill Yukine.
[TSUYU]
How is he?
Shouldn't simply
existing be a struggle
for a god of calamity
like him?
[YUKINE]
What?
Hold on a minute!
You're telling me
that those two worked together?
Does that mean--?
Is Yato a god of calamity too?
I didn't even know--
[KOFUKU] Yori knows
something about it.
[KOFUKU] I mentioned it
to her once before.
[DAIKOKU]
That's right.
And she didn't seem to have
any problems with it, either.
That girl.
She's one tough cookie, ya know?
Yatty's different
than he used to be.
Which is why Yori's
stuck by his side.
I think it's pretty
obvious at this point
that Yori really
loves you and Yatty.
[YUKINE]
I...
I have to get
her memories back for her.
[YATO]
She'll never remember me.
Not at this rate.
[TENJIN] Perhaps it's
for the best if she doesn't.
As I've said before, you should
cut your ties with her.
[TENJIN] Your connection
gives her too much
of a direct focus on
the events of our world.
It will eventually keep
her from living in her own.
Forgetting you could be
the best thing to happen to her.
She'll likely revert
back to her fully human state.
And she'll never
be happy as a half-Phantom.
[YATO walking]
[TSUYU] He appears to have
made up his mind.
[MAYU]
Poor Yato.
[water rushing]
[YUKINE]
Yato!
Where have you
been all night?
Listen to this.
I was thinking about
Hiyori's mem-
[YATO]
Forget it.
Just forget
about Hiyori.
What?
Hey!
Yato! Yato!
[hydraulics moving]
[RABO]
We must act quickly.
The longer we wait,
the more remorseless
the passage of
time becomes.
[NORA]
You worry too much.
[NORA] Yato will
return very soon.
I'm sure of it.
[KOFUKU]
And then!
[door slams]
Yukki!
Have you seen
Yatty yet?
[YUKINE]
What the hell?
What's wrong
with Yato now?
This doesn't make sense.
Why now?
[page flapping]
[HIYORI thinking]
I drew this.
But how?
The only way I could have
is if I do know him.
But if I do,
why can't I remember him?
[phone vibrating]
[HIYORI out loud]
It's Yukine.
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
[YUKINE panting]
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
[HIYORI]
No big.
So what's up?
[YUKINE]
For you.
Wow, a picture book!
So did you make it?
Can I read it
to you?
Uh-huh.
[YUKINE clears throat]
[YUKINE]
Here we go.
This is the
story of Yato,
the tracksuit-wearing god
and his friend Hiyori.
[YUKINE]
Now let the tale begin!
[YATO]
Dammit, Yukine.
He's with Hiyori again.
[YUKINE] And on his
very first try,
the gifted Regalia
drew a Borderline.
[HIYROI]
That's so cool!
You really are
amazing, Yukine.
Even Yato was surprised
when I did it.
Really?
He was?
Uh, yeah.
Moving on.
[NORA]
Yato.
Do you recognize this?
[YUKINE] So the ablution
was a success.
All thanks to
Yato and Hiyori.
[YUKINE] If neither of you
had been there for me.
Then I might not have
been able to come back.
[YUKINE]
And that's how...
[YUKINE trembling]
That's how...
[YUKINE] And that's how
Hiyori, Yato, and I...
[YUKINE]
...all became best friends.
[HIYORI clapping]
[HIYORI] I'm sorry,
but I still don't have
any memories
of Mr. Yato.
Although, it does sound like
we really are good friends.
Yeah!
So, I was wondering.
If you don't mind and all,
could I have that book?
Huh?
Uh, y'see,
the thing--
I just kind of
feel like
if I keep looking
at it over and over,
it might help me remember
what I've forgotten.
[YUKINE]
If you think so.
[NORA] The lunar cycle
is waning.
[NORA]
Tell me, Yato.
[NORA] Where do you suppose the
waning part of the moon goes?
[YATO]
Where does it go?
[water dripping]
[YUKINE]
You okay?
Hiyori--
[HIYORI]
Um.
Is this yours?
[train rattling]
[YUKINE panting]
[YATO groaning]
Yukine.
What the hell
have you done, Nora?
[NORA] Hiyori's memory
is waning bit by bit,
falling away
into total darkness.
If you don't come
see us, and soon,
[NORA] she'll end up as nothing
but an empty vessel.
[water rushing]
[YUKINE trembling]
Hiyori.
She's forgotten
about me now.
[YUKINE sobbing]
She doesn't remember me!
[YATO]
Yukine.
We're going to get
her memory back.
It's just...
Going up against
them again
could very likely
destroy you.
Yato.
[YATO] Not only that,
but I might give them
exactly what
they want.
[YUKINE] You have to
believe in yourself.
That is what you
told me, right?
[YUKINE sniffling]
[water flowing]
[pages flapping]
[HIYROI] Is that
supposed to be me?
Why do I have a tail?
[HIYORI'S MOM]
Hiyori!
Time to go!
[rain falling]
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
[HIYORI]
Uh, yeah?
[YUKINE]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have freaked out
on you like that earlier.
Really.
You're the one who's being
tormented through all this.
[YUKINE]
The thing is.
[YUKINE] We've dragged you into
something terrible.
[YUKINE]
Actually.
[YUKINE] It's Yato's crappy
history that's to blame here.
But, he is still my master,
and his problems are...
...well they're
my problems, too.
Do I have to do
all the talking?
[YATO] I promise that
we will get your memory back,
so you just
rest easy and wait.
Okay?
[YUKINE]
Hiyori?
What's wrong?
I'm actually
not sure.
I don't know why
I'm crying.
[YATO]
Enough of that.
Let's go.
[HIYORI gasping]
[ringing]
[wet thudding]
[rain falling]
[YATO singing]
Dun-duh-dun!
[YATO] It's time for
your Regalia midterms!
[YATO] List ten good
things about me!
[YUKINE]
Ten?
[YATO] You're already
failing! Try for five.
[YUKINE]
Five?
[YATO] Next time on Noragami:
"A Scrap of a Memory."
Fine, just the best three!
[YUKINE] I'm sorry, but
I can't think of any.
[YATO] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Are you serious?