[rain falling]
[thunder rolling]
[RABO] My shrine
has grown so neglected.
The world was once
ruled by strife
and filled with countless
vile wishes.
But the etchings here
are those that have
been long since fulfilled,
and callers come no more.
[NORA]
Rabo.
And yet... here I stand.
Still alive,
after all this time.
We two are gods
of calamity.
Where we are born
from chaos and suffering,
only to be reclaimed
by it.
[rock crumbles]
[RABO] Isn't that so,
Yato god?
[rock falling]
[rain falling]
[chimes ringing]
[BOTH]
Huh?
What?
[YATO]
You.
[YATO] Why did you come
along with us, you idiot?
[HIYORI]
Huh?
Where are we?
How did we
get here?
[HIYORI shreaking] And why
do I have a tail?
What's going on
here?
[YATO groaning]
Oh, man.
[RABO]
I'm pleased you've come.
[YATO grumbling]
[YATO]
Rabo.
[NORA] They seem to have brought
one uninvited guest.
I swear...
[NORA]
You are nothing but a nuisance.
[YATO]
Hiyori!
[HIYORI]
Huh?
[YATO] You need to get
far away from here!
[RABO]
Well, here we are.
Come at me!
[YATO]
Sekki!
[RABO]
Reiki!
[YATO yelling]
[chimes ring]
[RABO chuckles]
[YATO yelling]
[sword slashing]
[YATO] I will
make you return.
Hiyori's memories!
[bell ringing]
[YATO running]
[swords clashing]
[RABO stumbling]
[YUKINE]
We've got him!
[YATO yelling]
[RABO]
You're too slow!
[YATO groaning]
[water rushing]
[YATO gurgling]
[YATO struggling]
[YATO]
Dammit!
I can't break it
from the inside!
[sword sizzling]
[RABO sighes]
Furuhime.
[RABO] The true Yato god has
yet to return to us.
[YATO gurgling]
[HIYORI struggling]
[water splashing]
[BOTH groaning]
[YATO gasps]
[YUKINE]
Hiyori?
[HIYORI]
Ow, that hurt.
Hey, are you okay?
[YATO] Uh-huh. But what
the hell are you doing here?
Didn't I tell you to run?
[YATO grunts]
Still.
I appreciate it.
Sure.
[RABO] What is that
look on his face?
[RABO] That thawed, soft
expression.
[HIYORI whimpers]
[YATO grunting]
[swords clanging]
[RABO]
Where is he?
[YATO]
Huh?
The god of
calamity I knew!
[YATO groans]
[YATO grunts]
[YATO gasps]
[swords banging]
Where is the
true Yato?
Tell me!
[RABO] With those eyes aflame
with beautiful depravity.
Where is that Yato god?
That's the god of
calamity worthy
of crossing swords
with me!
[YATO]
Shut your mouth!
[swords clanging]
[YATO grunting]
[YATO yelling]
[RABO]
Now I see.
[YATO yelling]
You don't have the
right motivation.
I told you
to shut up!
What are you--?
[HIYORI whimpering]
[chimes ringing]
[NORA giggling]
[HIYORI whimpering]
[swords clanging]
[YATO panting]
[YATO]
Sekki!
[BOTH yell]
[NORA]
Well Rabo?
[MAYU] I've never seen a
Storm this massive.
[TSUYU]
This does not bode well.
[TENJIN grunting]
[BISHAMON yelling]
[gun shots]
[STINGRAY PHANTOM exploding]
[twinkling]
[KURAHA roaring]
[BISHAMON]
There's no end to them.
They just keep coming!
[BISHAMON]
Kazuma.
[KAZUMA]
Yes?
[BISHAMON] What did
Lady Kofuku tell you?
[BISHAMON]
I've got a feeling
that a Vent didn't
cause this Storm.
[KAZUMA]
You're right, Veena.
A Storm like this.
It is the product of
a god of calamity.
[BISHAMON]
A god of calamity?
[BOTH panting]
[water splashing]
[YATO]
Yukine!
[chimes ringing]
[YUKINE] What are we
gonna do here, Yato?
[YATO] I want you to take Hiyori
and get away from here.
[YUKINE] Huh?
[YATO] I'm the only one
that Rabo's concerned with.
I'll keep him busy while
you two get out of here.
[YUKINE] What,
you can't be serious?
[YUKINE] You're completely
unarmed without me!
[YATO]
Shut up!
I can handle this.
[water drips]
[YATO gasps]
[YUKINE]
What is that?
[YATO] It's the container
holding Hiyori's memories.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[RABO smirks]
[YATO gasps]
[YATO running]
[water splashing]
[YATO grunts]
[container shatters]
[YATO gasps]
[water splashing]
[NORA] Oh, how tragic.
[NORA] The mortal life is
just too fragile.
[rain falling]
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
[YATO gasps]
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
Please!
Wake up!
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
Yato! There's something
wrong with her!
Hiyori.
What do we do?
[clothes rustling]
[RABO] Forget the girl,
Yato god.
She's been reduced
to nothing more
than a mindless, hollow
container now.
Just an empty
sack of flesh.
[YATO sighs]
[rain falling]
[clothes rustling]
[YATO'S fist clentching]
[YATO]
Rabo.
[RABO] Have I awakened
your hatred?
[RABO]
Finally.
[RABO] Show me your
loathing, fierce deity.
Accept and embrace your
maelstrom of hate.
God of calamity, Yato!
Be quiet.
[YATO]
Sekki!
[chime ringing]
[sword slashing]
[RABO groaning]
[water splashing]
[wood crashing]
[rock crumbling]
[RABO grunting]
[wet footsteps]
[RABO]
There they are.
Those are the eyes.
Come!
You come to me
this time.
That grin on
your face?
I'm gonna carve it
into a frown.
[YUKINE]
Yato?
[RABO leaping]
[water splashing]
[swords clanging]
[swords rattling]
[wave crashing]
[rain falling]
[water splashes]
[RABO yelling]
[chime rings]
[swords clanging]
[BOTH grunting]
[water crashing]
[RABO smirking]
[RABO]
This takes me back.
The sky is roiling above
us just as when we lived.
[swords slashing]
[RABO]
We are gods of calamity.
Fierce deities devoted
to heinous wishes and driven
to soak the Near Shore
in the blood of innocence.
[YATO]
Enough talk.
[RABO]
This is it.
The moment I've
been waiting for.
The moment that my very
own wish comes to pass!
[waves crashing]
[YATO yells]
[RABO] My earthly name
is Rabo.
Bearing a posthumous
name, I don this mask.
And proclaim myself
a spirit vessel!
[RABO] Ye names that assemble
cannot defy me.
You are bound and beholden
to my every order!
Submit yourselves
to me!
And obey the mask!
Now gather depravity!
[wind howling]
[YUKINE]
The Storm.
He's absorbing it!
[RABO grunting]
[YATO]
You damn fool.
Are you completely
insane?
Merging your being
with Phantoms?
[RABO demonic voice]
Insane?
Of course not.
I've taken
this action.
In order to fight you
to the death!
[YUKINE gasps]
[swords clanging]
[wind rushing]
[wind howling]
[RABO demonicly yells]
[YATO grunts]
[rock exploding]
[YATO yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
[swords clanging]
[YATO grunts]
[YUKINE gasping]
[YUKINE]
Yato!
Look!
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
[rocks falling]
[YATO grunting]
[explosive wind]
[explosion]
[rocks splashing]
[water moving]
[HIYORI thinking]
What's happened to me?
Where am I?
Who am I?
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
This smell.
It seems so familiar.
[YUKINE]
Yato!
You okay?
[YUKINE groaning]
[YUKINE]
Rabo.
He's coming for us!
[YUKINE]
Yato!
Wake up!
[YUKINE echoing]
Yato!
[HIYORI thinking]
It smells so nice.
I know I've smelled it
somewhere before.
I know it because...
... it's my favorite smell.
[clothes rustling]
[YATO gasps]
[water dripps]
[HIYORI groans]
[HIYORI]
Hey why are you crying?
Yato.
[YATO]
You...
You know me.
[YUKINE gasps]
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
[YATO laughing]
[HIYORI]
Huh?
You're okay!
You're back!
Ha!
Hiyori!
Thank you!
Wh-wh-wh-wha?
[HIYORI shrieking] Get off of me
you creepy deadbeat!
[YATO screaming]
[NORA] She broke my spell
completely on her own.
She shouldn't have been
able to uncork her memories
[NORA]
How did she?
[HIYORI]
You cretin!
I expected more
from you!
[YATO]
Hiyori.
You called me...
... by my name.
So?
[YUKINE]
Her memory's back!
She knows us!
Well yeah.
Why wouldn't I
know you guys?
[HIYORI screaming]
[YATO]
Hiyori!
[HIYORI screams]
[HIYORI grunts]
[chime ringing]
[RABO demonic voice]
What will it take
to make you return
to your old self?
We are gods
of calamity!
We grant depraved wishes
and feed upon
human greed and hate--
So what?
Quit bringin' up
the past!
It doesn't mean
anything now!
[YATO]
Let Hiyori go!
[RABO snarling]
[RABO demonic voice]
It's all your fault.
You're to blame
for his pathetic state!
A pitiful half-Phantom.
You will serve as a
sacrifice for my power!
[YATO]
Sekki!
[chime rings]
We're taking
him out.
[YUKINE]
Huh?
We'll hit Hiyori
from this distance-
It's just like
a Borderline.
[YATO] Rabo's absorbed
a Storm and merged
[YATO] with the
Phantoms within.
It's up to you to draw
the line between
who gets killed
and who survives.
[YUKINE]
What?
It's up to me?
[HIYORI whimpers]
[YATO grunts]
[YATO] You can
do this, Yukine.
[YUKINE grunts]
[YATO]
We can do this.
Together!
[RABO snarling]
[YATO] This is the land
of the rising son.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me.
I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki
and expel thy
vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
[RABO grunts]
[sword slashes]
[water splashing]
[YATO]
Rend!
[water bubbling]
[twinkling]
[thunder]
[HIYORI screams]
[RABO grunting]
[RABO screaming]
[twinkling]
[HIYORI coughing]
[HIYORI sobbing, running]
[HIYORI]
Yato!
[YATO]
Hiyori!
You alright?
Let's go home.
Please take me home.
[HIYORI]
Yato!
[RABO]
Yato.
[YATO] You have
made a wish.
Ya-Yato.
And it's been heard
loud and clear.
[RABO]
Yato god!
[chime echoes]
[water splashes]
[RABO faintly]
Yato god.
[YUKINE]
His face!
[YATO] Just
as I thought.
You used a curse
to maintain
your disintegrating
form.
But why?
[RABO] It doesn't matter
how many wishes we grant them.
People always loathe
gods of calamity,
and ultimately,
they forget about us.
[RABO] For better
or worse, humans
will always
be fickle creatures.
That is the way
of things.
It is our
inescapable fate
to be slain
by their disregard.
And so, when I awoke
from my 500 year slumber...
...I yearned to be killed.
Not by the ignorance
of man,
but by the hand of one
who does truly know me...
...by you.
[YATO] You've always
been such a downer.
And now,
Yato god...
I go first.
First into the depths
of fate
that you and I
are bound to share.
Except that I'm
nothing like you.
[faint booming]
[wind rushing]
[BISHAMON]
A god has been slain.
[TENJIN]
Another god lost.
[water drips]
[NORA sighs]
[NORA] Well,
that was a massive failure.
[NORA] I guess I'd better go
home and speak with Father.
[YUKINE] So you remember
everything?
[YUKINE]
You remember me and Yato?
[HIYORI]
Yep!
[YUKINE laughing]
I've gotta ask though.
How did you just suddenly
get your memory back?
[HIYORI]
Huh?
It was because of
Yato's...
...his smell.
[YUKINE]
His what?
[HIYORI]
Uh.
Never mind, forget it,
it's nothing!
Yeah, I don't know how!
I can't remember
at all!
[HIYORI laughing]
[YUKINE slowly]
Okay.
What's up?
[YATO]
Hiyori.
Okay, you're all
serious now.
Just listen.
I think it's for the best
if you cut all ties with us.
That's the only way you'll
really live a happy life.
So.
[YUKINE]
What?
Hey, hold on!
No, I'm not
gonna do that.
We're friends.
There's no way I'd be happy
without you guys in my life.
[KOFUKU]
Wow!
[KOFUKU] Yatty and Yukki really
mean that much to you?
[KOFUKU]
Are you sure about that?
[YATO] She's just being stubborn
for the sake of being stubborn.
[HIYORI]
That is not true.
I mean it.
I'm not turning
my back on you.
I wanna be with
you forever.
You're the only one who wants
to cut ties here, Yato.
[KOFUKU laughing]
How romantic!
[DAIKOKU]
We need booze!
It's time to celebrate!
[HIYORI]
Uh, wait!
I didn't mean I wanna
be with you forever like that,
not in that way!
[YATO] I'll grant
your wish...
...for five yen.
Pay up!
[HIYORI giggles]
You've made a wish and it's
been heard, loud and clear.
Hiyori Iki.
May our fates
forever intertwine.