[FEMALE STUDENT 1 thinking]
Man, tests really suck.
[MALE STUDENT 1 thinking]
I have to ace this.
[MALE STUDENT 2 thinking] I just
want to get out of this place.
Should've studied harder!
[FEMALE STUDENT 2 thinking]
Look at her.
Does she think
she's too cool for us?
[FEMALE STUDENT 3]
I just need to pass.
[MALE STUDENT 3 thinking]
You're a loser.
Nobody cares about you.
[FEMALE STUDENT 4 thinking]
I failed. I know I failed.
[FEMALE STUDENT 5 thinking] She
misses a little bit of school,
and now she's getting
all this special treatment?
Please!
[FEMALE STUDENT 6 thinking]
Pathetic.
Why does she even bother living?
She's just a waste of space.
[ALL]
You really do suck.
[GIRL gasps]
[GIRL thinking]
Help me!
Oh, god, please help me!
[ding]
[YATO] Payment received.
You have made a wish,
and it's been heard,
loud and clear!
[MAYU] Uh, does this Phantom
seem especially large to you?
It is exam season.
Everyone's on edge.
But with you I can
take this thing easily.
Ready to go, Tomone?
I'm ready when you are.
Alright then, let's do it!
Hey there, fish face,
how ya doin'?
[YATO grunting]
[FISH PHANTOM growling]
This is the land
of the rising sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
I now lay thee waste
with the Hanki,
and expel thy vast defilement!
Rend!
[FISH PHANTOM growling]
[YATO panting]
Bye now!
That the best you can do?
Didn't even break a sweat.
[TOMONE] Hey, Yato, aren't
you forgetting something?
Oh!
Revert, Tomone.
[TOMONE grunts and sniffs]
Ugh. Didn't break
a sweat, huh?
[YATO yelps]
Show some respect, huh?
[YATO growling]
I'm your master!
Actually, we need
to talk about that.
I'm quitting.
I won't be your
Regalia anymore.
Uh, you're just
kidding, right?
It's only been
like three months--
[TOMONE yelling]
It felt like three years!
I can't take it anymore!
Living like a vagrant
with a minor god
who doesn't even
have his own shrine!
I can't do it!
No!
Huh?
[TOMONE crying]
Hey, shouldn't I be
the one who's crying here?
Fine!
Stop wailing already!
I can take a hint.
It's over.
I hereby release you.
[TOMONE sighs]
That's so much better!
And just so you know,
the usual practice
is to give at least
a full month's notice
before you quit.
It's common courtesy.
As if you deserve
any courtesy.
Later, loser!
You're just an aimless
drifter in a tracksuit
who likes to play
at being a god.
Damn you!
Don't you dare come
crawling back once I hit it big!
Just you wait and see!
Soon enough I'll have
120 million worshippers,
and all the other
gods will envy me!
You ungrateful wretch!
[YATO sneezes]
A-choo!
[dog yapping]
[YATO]
That fickle wench.
I can't believe
a Regalia actually quit on me.
[YATO sighs]
Ow, my neck.
This is gettin' old.
Pretty meager savings.
I'll never have
a shrine, will I?
Oh, well.
finding a new
Regalia comes first.
God or not, without
a Regalia I'm unarmed.
No, worse than that,
I'm essentially naked!
I can't go out on
any jobs like this!
Of course, it's not like
I've got a ton of work, anyway.
[cell phone rings]
Hello there, and
thank you for calling!
Fast and affordable, Delivery
God Yato at your service!
Huh?
Milord has gone missing?
That's awful!
[HIYORI] Milord, huh?
[AMI] That's quite a name.
Some people are really
weird about their pets.
[YAMA] I guess "Milord" is
better than "my god," right?
[GIRLS laughing]
Cute cat, though.
Ami here's no better
than these people.
She named her dog
after Zenny's leader.
What's so bad about that?
Shiina's totally
the love of my life!
Yeah, whatever.
I'm all about
the Hundred Archfiends.
I don't understand how
you can like that stuff.
[YATO yelling]
Milord! Where are you?
Here, kitty!
Come to Yato!
Well, which do you think
is more godlike, Hiyori?
[HIYORI] Want to see
the man I worship?
[CROWD cheering]
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
We've entered the final round
of the showdown of
the century, folks!
The fighters are circling and--
Look at that!
He goes for the leg!
How will Tono respond?
There it is!
His patented
Jungle Savate technique!
Sorry.
Obviously you were the wrong
person to ask about this.
I didn't know you
liked martial arts.
Are you a closet fan?
Well, I wouldn't say
I'm a closet fan, exactly.
You haven't told
your parents, right?
Uh, no.
I'm fairly certain
my mom's head would explode
if she found out
I'm into this stuff.
[YATO] Here, Milord!
Where are you?
Are you back there? Milord!
Where be'est thou?
Here, kitty, kitty!
[HIYORI] Okay, stop it!
That's plain freaky!
You two sound just like her!
[GIRLS giggling]
[AMI] Anyway, Hiyori, are
there any guys you do like?
Besides Tono, of course.
[YAMA]
Yeah!
Like someone
closer to our age
who isn't
a famous fighter.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
Well, um...
Someone I like...
Let's see...
No, I don't think
there is anybody.
[HIYORI gasps]
[YATO breaths in deeply]
[YATO squeals]
[YATO]
There you are!
Hey, no! Come back!
Don't you run off!
Milord! Wait!
[bus horn honking]
Beeeeeep!
[tires squeling]
[YAMA]
Hiyori?
[AMI screams]
[MALE BYSTANDER 1A]
Hey! What happened?
[MALE BYSTANDER 1B] A girl
jumped in front of that bus!
[HIYORI panting]
Running into
the street like that?
What kind of
an idiot are you?
You realize you
could've been killed?
Well hey, uh...
...aren't you
missing something?
Hiyori? Hiyori?
Can you hear me? Hiyori!
Say something!
[FEMALE BYSTANDER 1A]
Is she still breathing?
[MALE BYSTANDER 1C]
I called for an ambulance.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
Huh?!
[ambulence siren wailing]
[HIYORI'S MOM]
Hiyori?
Please be okay!
Hiyori!
Her eyes are opening!
[HIYORI'S DAD]
Thank goodness you're awake!
We were so worried!
How do you feel?
Are you in pain?
Don't just stand there,
dear, examine her!
Oh, of course!
Good, everything
looks normal.
[GIRLS and MOM sigh]
[GIRLS]
Unbelievable!
So I'm okay, Dad?
Well, your CAT scan
looked just fine,
and your EEG
appears normal, too.
Considering you
were hit by a bus,
it's a miracle you only
wound up with a few scratches.
A bus hit me?
Whatever the tests say,
I'm still worried.
If anything should happen
to our precious Hiyori.
We should keep her here
for observation.
It is our hospital.
Come, now, dear.
There's a list of patients
waiting to be admitted.
Even so.
[HIYORI]
What about the other guy?
What happened to him?
Yeah another person.
I think I saw someone.
What?
Nobody else was there, though.
Hiyori was just suddenly
lying in the street.
Are you sure?
[HIYORI's dad] You've
been through a trauma.
Maybe your memory's
still a bit hazy.
I'm sure there
was somebody there!
[HIYORI's MOM]
Oh, my poor dear.
You must be exhausted.
Why don't you get some rest?
[HIYORI thinking]
He was there.
He was.
I'm sure of it,
and there's more.
I remember.
Another me, like
I was outside my body.
[MALE VOICE 1A]
I don't want to die.
It's not fair!
[MALE VOICE 1B]
Where is she?
[FEMALE VOICE 1A]
Please let me see him!
[GIRL VOICE 1A] When will I get
to leave? I hate it here!
[GIRL VOICE 1B]
I'm really scared... Mommy!
It hurts.
It hurts so much!
[GIRL VOICE 1B] Please
just make it stop hurting!
[FEMALE VOICE 1C] We can leave
when you're all better, okay?
[Hiyori thinking]
These voices.
What are they?
[GIRL VOICE 1A]
I can't breathe!
[GIRL VOICE 1B]
It hurts, Mommy!
[FEMALE VOICE 1B] I just want
to go outside for a little bit.
[MALE VOICE 1A]
It's hopeless.
[YATO] You hear the
voices of the Far Shore?
[HIYARI screams]
Doesn't look like you
got hurt too bad, huh?
[HIYARI] The guy
from earlier!
Thanks for that,
by the way.
'Course, I didn't need
help avoiding that bus,
but no human has ever
tried to save me before.
I don't get it.
Who are you?
That's easy.
I'm a god.
Hello, police?
There's an intruder
in my hospital room.
I think he
might be crazy.
He says he's a god--
Wait, hang up the phone!
I'm not crazy.
I really am one
of the gods, okay?
I am the god Yato.
A god called Yato?
What are
you playing at?
I've never heard
of that god.
Not once in
my whole life!
[YATO gasps]
[YATO exhales]
Well, that's understandable.
I'm still what you might
call an up-and-comer.
But just wait!
Before much longer, the whole
world will know my name!
I'll be mega famous.
The go-to god!
The god that
everybody prays to!
Awesome, aren't I?
Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
I'll be the
highest god in the land!
Me! Yato!
[EVERYONE cheering]
[YATO giggling]
[YATO coughing]
It's gonna be
real stormy tonight.
This place is already
crawling with 'em,
and I'm Regalia-less,
so I can't stick around.
Somebody else is
already using Nora tonight.
Hey! That's one of
my get-well gifts!
By the way,
what's your name?
Uh, it's Hiyori.
Hiyori Iki.
[HIYORI gasps]
Hiyori Iki, huh?
I came to make
sure you're okay,
and you seem to be just fine.
So, we're even now.
Huh?
See ya!
Wait!
[HIYORI thinking]
My body feels so heavy...
Can't stay awake...
Yato...
[AMI]
Hiyori!
Ami! Yama!
Hey, you guys!
[YAMA] So, you're
all healed up, then?
Yep!
You scared us!
Glad you didn't
die or anything.
I'll try never to
do it again, I swear.
Yeah, stay away
from buses from now on.
Or you'll see my version
of a Jungle Savate!
I bet she wouldn't mind
a good smack
from her dear Tono!
You're probably right!
Whoa, hey,
easy there!
Whoops. I'm sorry.
I've just started getting these
sudden attacks of drowsiness.
Huh?
Don't stay up so late
playing video games.
[HIYORI laughs uncomfortably]
[HIYORI thinking] I don't know,
maybe it was just a dream.
[HIYORI sighs]
It felt so real,
that night in the hospital.
I could have
sworn I met somebody.
[whistle blowing]
Tracksuits...
[AMI] You sure
you're okay, Hiyori?
[YAMA] Yeah,
what's going on?
You've been kinda
out of it all day.
[HIYORI] Sorry, like I said
before, I'm just sleepy.
Maybe you should
still be in the hospital.
It hasn't been long
since the accident.
What is it?
Why'd you stop?
[AMI] Hmm? Oh,
that cat again?
[HIYORI thinking]
That's right.
That day, there
was some strange guy
in a tracksuit chasing a cat.
Milord, where are you?
I'm sorry, you guys.
Go on without me.
Huh?
[AMI and YAMA]
[HIYORI]
I shall stay.
I must endeavor to
locate Milord forthwith.
What?
[AMI and YAMA]
[HIYORI]
Come here, Milord!
Who's a good kitty?
That's not him.
Not there, either.
Milord, where are you hiding?
[HIYORI thinking]
If I can just find the cat,
maybe it'll trigger
a buried memory.
[HIYORI yelling]
Milord! Here, boy!
Come on out, kitty!
[HIYORI sighs]
[HIYORI stumbles]
I feel so sleepy again.
What is that strange smell?
[wind whoosing]
[YATO]
Milord!
Come on out now, kitty!
Come on!
I've got some
nice catnip for you!
[wind whoosing]
Better find him fast.
It's getting stormy out.
[cat meowing]
[YATO]
Huh?
[cat meowing]
[cat hissing]
Milord!
Hold on, just stay there!
There's no need to run.
[MILORD hissing]
What's the matter, boy?
[FROG PHANTOMS]
Smells nice.
[PHANTOMS whispering]
Smells nice...
Just small ones,
but there are too many of them.
The numbers aren't
on my side, here!
You provoked them,
didn't you?
Just like a cat!
[MILORD meows]
Milord, you know
what they say
about curiosity
and cats, don't you?
[YATA panting]
[FROG PHANTOM 1A]
Smells nice.
[FROG PHANTOM 1A roars]
[MILORD meows in terror]
And in you go.
[FROG PHANTOM 1A roars]
A lot of good that did.
Hanki!
Come!
Oh, crap!
I forgot I don't
have a Regalia.
[FROG PHANTOM 1A growls]
[HIYORI whimpering]
[YATO thinking]
This chick again?
[HIYORI and YATO scream]
What is that thing?
[HIYORI and YATO grunting]
[HIYORI growls]
You want
a piece of me?
You idiot! Don't--
[HIYORI screaming]
Let's go!
Jungle Savate!
[FROG PHANTOM 1A crying]
Whoa! It worked!
The great Tono
has blessed me
with a fraction
of his mighty power!
Oh!
I'll be your devoted
follower forever, my lord!
I think we
finally lost it.
[YATO thinking]
This girl saved me again.
I can't freakin'
believe it.
[HIYORI] I'm glad I was able
to track you down, Yato.
I had a lot of questions
to ask you, you know,
but you just
suddenly ran off on me.
No dodging my
questions this time.
I want some
straight answers!
Uhh, sorry,
but your soul?
It's slipped out.
What?
Huh?
If you want your body,
it's back over there.
Wha--?
How's that possible?
Wh-What happened?
Does this mean
that I'm dead?
That's not it exactly.
It's more like your body's
just taking a nap.
[MILORD meows]
Look what you've done.
I thought black cats were
supposed to be unlucky.
[KEIICHI'S MOM]
I'll hand out fliers
and look around
some more tomorrow.
Okay?
Don't worry, sweetie.
I'm sure he'll turn up.
[doorbell rings]
[KEIICHI]
Hello?
[MILORD meows]
You came home!
Mom, it's Milord!
He came back!
Can you believe it?
My wish really came true!
Thanks, Yato!
You're the best ever!
[MILORD meows]
[HIYORI thinking]
That smells nice.
[HIYORI yelling]
Hey, what are you doing?
Put me down, you creep!
I'm not a creep!
I'm a god!
Yeah, about that,
why do I have a--
Hey, it's gone.
I swear I had a tail.
Was it all a dream?
That has to be it.
What's going on with me?
I don't understand
any of this.
It must be a result
of the accident.
There's the Near Shore,
where the living reside,
then there's the Far Shore.
Somehow or other, you've wound
up in the divide between them.
The Near Shore
and the Far Shore?
Yeah.
As for the Far Shore,
what would you humans call it?
The afterlife, I guess.
See, you're still
technically alive,
but you're also a Phantom.
What's a Phantom?
Basically, they're incarnations
of emotional energy.
They possess people
and cause a lot of trouble.
So that giant frog earlier.
That was one of
these "Phantoms"?
Yeah, that's right.
[HIYORI screams] You
mean I'm like that thing?
Well, no, not
exactly like it.
Actually, I'd describe
you more as "on the fence."
And that means what?
All this is
way over my head!
Well, for one thing, you'll
probably lose your body a lot.
Okay, and how do
I make that stop?
Well... I'm not
sure you can.
This is just
the way you are now.
Best accept it.
Accept it?
I can't live like this!
It's not fair!
Turn me back!
You keep on saying
you're a god, right?
So help me!
All right. Pay up.
Gods charge money now?
Of course we do!
Nobody's gonna
grant a wish for nothing!
This is the going
rate for one wish.
What? 550,000?!
I can't afford that much!
Tch. Stupid mortal.
I am a god, you know?
And what do you offer
when you petition the gods?
That's right!
A 5 yen coin!
What? 5?
Uh, okay.
You have made a wish,
and it's been heard,
loud and clear!
Hiyori Iki.
Thus is it done,
may our fates intertwine.
[YATO] Step one in Operation
Make Yato a Major God:
come up with a new chant
for litter-bearers.
[HIYORI] Why won't the
regular old "heave-ho" work?
Instead of "heave-ho"
let's go with "ya-ho."
Next time on Noragami:
"Snow-like."
Remember, it's
"Ya-ho, Yato!"