March 1st, 18 years ago.
On my way home, I saw Kayo standing alone in the park.
I guess it was a little before 6:00.
That night I was on my way to the hideout.
I think it was to try and find my gloves.
But I don't remember if I found them there or not.
After I left, I saw Yuuki sitting by himself on the bank,
looking out at the river.
On the way back home,
I took a shortcut that took me by the park again.
But this time when I looked in, Kayo was gone.
Let's talk about averages.
A week from now, Kayo will be the first
victim in a series of kidnappings and murders.
Day X.
If I can get her to survive March 1st
and spend the 2nd with me at my birthday party,
that should be enough to change her future.
I'm not gonna let her die.
Good morning, you sleepy head.
Morning.
Up and at 'em. Food's almost ready.
OK.
Thanks for breakfast.
Uh, hey, Mom?
Hmm?
I was thinking of going out this Saturday.
Like on a date?
No! I was gonna go to the
Science Center with some friends.
Oh, well. If it were a date, I'd give you spending cash.
Shit, for real?
It is a date, isn't it?
Mm‐hmm.
Then bring her by. I'd love to meet her.
We can have hotpot or something.
Actually, I invited Kayo to the party.
Oh. Kayo from a few streets over, huh?
Damn, she's good at getting info out of people.
You can go. Just be safe.
Thanks, Mom.
Hurry up and finish your breakfast, kiddo.
Mm‐hmm.
Stand... bow.
Bye!
Liveman's gonna be on. Cool, huh?
What's a falcon? It's a bird, duh!
You're so smart.
This Saturday, Kayo's not staying home.
I'm gonna take her away from her mom and the beatings.
Mr. Yashiro?
Um, sir?
What's up, guys?
Can you explain this? I don't get it.
Sure. Hmm. That's a tough one.
What a bunch of flirty little tramps.
Ecch.
What are you talking about? It's not
like you never did that too, you know.
Instead of dissing him, go up
there and show him who's boss.
What's "dis" mean? You trying to sound cool?
Oh! Gotta watch what I say.
The teacher doesn't care about
me anymore, he thinks I'm a thief.
Bet you do, too.
Not that I care.
Hey, guys, I got an idea.
Oh, yeah? What is it?
Um, let's go to the Science Center on Saturday.
I'll ask Kayo to go, too.
Yeah, that's a great idea!
Ohhh!
I can't make it.
Sorry, but I've already made plans that day.
Oh, really?
Uh, same for me, too, dude.
I, uh, got some important things need doing.
Yeah, what he said. I'd like
to go, but I can't either. Sorry.
Yeah, me too.
Oh.
It's better if it's just you and Kayo anyway.
See ya.
Satoru, everything OK?
Oh, yeah.
I told them I couldn't hang out
Saturday 'cause I had a date with you.
What a lie.
I did it again.
But... my mom wants me to get home early Saturday, so...
I just wanna take you someplace cool.
I'll ask her and get permission.
Kenya.
Could I see you in the faculty office for a sec?
No way. You kids are too young to go out on a date.
But it's more like a field trip. We'll be learning stuff.
You can stay home and learn stuff.
Besides, Kayo helps me around the house Saturdays.
Oh, yeah, with what?
Blowing off steam? Your right hook?
Little smart ass, I don't have to tell you a damn thing.
I just wanna know why you don't want Kayo to go with me.
I got a zillion reasons why.
First, you guys are too young to be dating.
Second, who's responsible if something happens? You?
Don't even go there with me, bitch.
What's your problem?
What do you get out of taking her anywhere?
She's just a gloomy little girl.
I'm not getting anything. All I want's to keep her safe!
Safe, huh?
What do you think you're keeping her safe from?
You her knight in shining armor?
Goddamn it.
Now she knows I know she beats on her.
What do you want to do, Kayo? You wanna go out with him?
Uggh! You're not going anywhere, you slut!
Mom!
Watch it, Ms. Hinazuki.
You shouldn't say nasty things
like that about your daughter.
Ms. Fujinuma, I...
This isn't any of your business.
Actually, half of this is my business.
A trip to the Science Center
can be very educational for a kid.
Don't you think we should encourage that?
We are their parents.
I'm a single mom, too, so I know how tough it can get.
Come by sometime and we'll talk.
Kayo, get inside.
OK.
So, Saturday, I'll see you then.
Did I screw everything up?
No. You were great.
Guess it's lucky I showed up when I did.
I got off work early and saw you,
so naturally I had to follow you.
What do you mean "naturally"?
Oh, nothing. I'm just kidding, is all.
Anyway, you don't have to worry about Kayo tonight.
Did you notice how nice her clothes were?
Her mom goes to a lot of trouble
to make her look presentable.
Do you know what's going on over there?
I didn't, but after what I just heard and saw,
I have my suspicions.
My mom wasn't a reporter for nothing.
Kayo's a cutie, isn't she?
Uh...
Dude, you're 29!
Hang in there, kiddo, for her.
I will.
It's Saturday, February the 27th.
It's sunny and clear, and for the last couple days,
Kayo's mom hasn't beaten her up, just like my mom said.
Lookit, he's my friend.
You're an idiot.
Isn't this place the coolest? I love it!
I think we're the only ones here.
When it's quiet like this, I pretend I snuck in.
Then, if someone comes, I hide from them.
Huh. She didn't call me an idiot.
Take a look inside this thing.
You wanna check out the next show in the planetarium?
We already saw enough stars on the mountain.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, I have to use the bathroom.
OK. I'll be here.
What the heck was that feeling back there?
It was like déjà vu.
I remember coming here a lot,
but this is my first time with Kayo.
I'm back.
Satoru, thanks for inviting me to come today.
Did you know that I like to come here, too?
Wait, did I?
Is that why I chose it?
Or... is this someplace special for me/you,
'cause like I/you wanna make manga and stuff?
We talked about the same thing 18 years ago.
Now I remember.
I came here by myself and ran into Kayo.
What's wrong?
Oh, uh, maybe...
Am I just repeating things?
Have I been doing it unconsciously this
whole time and... not changing the future at all?
Hey, Kayo, lemme carry that.
OK.
But there's so much that has changed
because of what I did different.
I can change the future.
I can.
Satoru...
I'm glad I had the guts to come today.
Mm‐hmm.
Hey, guys.
Hi, Kayo.
What's up?
I finished the stuff I had to do early.
Sorry we got here so late.
There, it changed.
Is it OK we came?
Yeah, of course it is.
Right, Kayo?
Mm‐hmm.
Hey, wanna hold our coats, too?
Hi, Satoru. Good morning.
Oh, hey, Kayo. Morning.
Yes! She's here on time on a Monday.
Damn, you're pretty.
Uh...
Oh, my God.
No way!
Satoru's so rad!
They're gonna get married!
They gotta get engaged first, ya lame‐brain.
What's "engaged" mean?
Congrats, you guys.
Settle down. Let's do some learning today.
Tomorrow's the day Kayo disappears.
March 1st.
The moment of truth.
Later, Hiromi.
Yep, see you tomorrow.
Hey, Kayo, wanna walk to school together?
I could swing by your place.
OK.
Mom.
Hello.
I'll come and get you tomorrow morning. Bye!
See you later, Mom.
OK.
I left the house a little early.
It's March 1st, 1988.
Kayo was kidnapped 18 years ago today.
It's me, Kayo.
But things are different now.
Good morning, Satoru.
Good morning.
No one's gonna hurt her.
Bye, Ms. Hinazuki.
A lot of things have changed
between this time 18 years ago and now.
They're holding hands and everything now.
Kayo was targeted because she
was always alone at the park.
But she's not alone anymore.
You guys are all still coming over tomorrow night, right?
Yeah.
Of course.
Yep.
She's had friends to hang out with the past few days.
I know. Wanna go play a game?
Uh...
And today she's with me.
I kind of wanted to get home early today.
Come on, don't be like that. We'll have fun.
OK.
It'll be fine.
Looks like I won again.
You're good.
This sucks.
Satoru, I should be getting home.
Yeah. It's getting late.
It's snowing.
I'll come by tomorrow, too.
See you in the morning!
Bye.
I said it loud like that on purpose.
That way, everyone heard me.
Kayo, her mom, and anyone else who might be out there.
They know I'm here now.
Day X is almost over. It's too good to be true.
I'm such a dumb ass.
Like this is gonna change anything.
I did it!
The day's over.
I changed history.
Good morning, Mom.
What the...? It's not even 6:00.
I know. Bye!
What about breakfast?!
I couldn't sleep after I got home.
I wanted to see Kayo again, no matter how early it was.
Morning. Sleep well?
You're an idiot.
Are you guys still on for tonight?
Yeah, dude, you know it.
If there's one thing I like
more than cake, it's birthday cake.
Cool. You guys want to hit the market with me...?
Hey!Satoru, Kayo. I need your
help putting these boxes away.
Huh? Can't it wait till tomorrow?
It sort of figures.
We blew off the last time we had cleaning duties.
I guess. Man, this is heavy.
Some friends they turned out to be.
Those doofuses totally bailed on us.
That'll be 5,000 yen, please.
OK.
Wait a sec. It cost 5,000 back then, too.
I remember I was so stoked about it being my birthday,
I spent all I had.
We made a ton of sandwiches, but since it
was just my mom and me, we had a lot left over.
I'm home.
Ready and...
Kayo, Satoru!
Happy birthday, guys!
Wait. Mom, you knew about this?
I helped out a little,
but they're the real masterminds behind this evil scheme.
So then, today, those chores were planned, too?
Uh‐huh. We asked Mr. Yashiro to stall you.
He also told us it was Kayo's birthday today.
I guess our little surprise worked, huh?
Uh, yeah.
Guess what, Kayo.
Satoru insisted on getting a cake just for you.
I'm sorry, Satoru. I tried.
But I couldn't finish your present in time.
Seriously? You were making me something?
Mm‐hmm.
That's why she wanted to get home early yesterday.
Last night, I fell asleep before I could finish it.
That's OK.
You can give it to me later.
Hey, guys.
Let's make 5,000 yen worth of sandwiches!
What?
You spent all the money?
We all had a blast making those sandwiches together.
But this time, there weren't any
left over at the end of the night.
Friends are the best, no doubt.
Everyone brought presents for Kayo and me.
Talk about a haul. And then...
That's from me.
Thank you, Satoru.
Thank you, everyone.
You can leave the cleaning up to us.
Yeah. Walk Kayo home.
It's so cold!
You're an idiot.
G‐Good night.
Here. Thank you for today.
I'm glad I got to be friends with you and the others.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
Promise.
Mm‐hmm. Can't wait.
Good night.
I did it. I did it.
It worked!
I changed history.
Everyone had left by the time I got home.
I was so exhausted from the past few days,
all that built‐up tension finally popped.
I collapsed on my futon and slept like a log.
Son of a bitch, I'm late!
I'm here, sir, sorry!
Just in time. I was about to mark you tardy.
Made it.
OK. Does anyone know if Kayo's coming today?
Kayo didn't show up that day. Or the next one.
And that promise she made me...
she never got to keep it.