Satoru Fujinuma, you're under arrest for
murder, attempted murder, and arson.
It's him.
It can't end like this.
I can't let it.
There's still something I have to do.
Move it.
Go back.
Go back!
Just once more!
Please.
Please!
Go baaaaack!
I'm glad I had the guts to come today.
So am I.
I'm real glad.
You're an idiot.
- ‐ Hey, guys.
- ‐ Hi, Kayo.
‐What's up?
‐I finished the stuff I had to do early.
- ‐Sorry we got here so late.
- ‐ Is it OK we came?
Yeah, of course it is.
Right, Kayo?
I have to pull this off.
This time I will.
Definitely.
I'm gonna do whatever it takes,
no matter how drastic, to change things,
'cause I know I won't get another chance.
This is my last Revival.
‐ Man, I'm starving.
‐ Let's go eat, then.
I don't got any money.
Oh, I do. My allowance should cover all of us.
How about okonomiyaki?
‐Whoo‐hoo!
‐You rock, man!
All right!
Hey, Satoru,
have you read that book I let you borrow yet?
Poe's "The Switched Man."
I gave it to you last week.
Oh, right. I haven't yet.
No.
I don't remember him loaning me a book back then.
It's a cool story.
When you get home, check it out.
I'm back.
Hey there, kiddo.
Dinner will be ready in a minute.
Hope you brought your appetite.
What's wrong, Satoru?
Go on, wash your hand...
Did you and Kayo have a fight?
No. It's nothing.
OK.
Well, go wash up.
Mom,
if you ever feel like going to Ueno...
remember,
you don't have to change trains to get there.
I'll keep that in mind.
February 29th, 1988.
The day before Kayo was supposed to be
kidnapped and murdered by a serial killer.
This is my third time around.
You’re holding hands and everything now!
It was the 28th when he said that before.
This time it's all or nothing.
Kenya,
I'm sorry, but...
I think I lost that book you loaned me.
You didn't lose it.
I never gave it to you.
The book's not real.
I made it up.
Can I talk to you in private?
Lately...
How do I say this?
Lately I noticed a change in how you are with people.
It feels like you care now.
You've always been friendly,
but before it sort of seemed like you were,
I don't know, faking it.
I could tell you were trying
hard to get along with everyone.
Anyway,
I like the new you better.
So after all that, the reason I wanted to
talk to you is 'cause I have a question.
Satoru, who are you?
It's like you've turned into a totally different person.
Or like there's a totally different person inside you now.
I realized it a few days ago,
when I saw you staring at Kayo during class.
I've seen bruises on her a bunch of times before.
But I never said anything to anyone about it.
I guess
I didn't think it was any of my business.
But when you noticed what was going on with her,
you actually did something.
That took guts.
You decided to help her without a second thought.
You did what I was scared to.
Come on,
tell me who you really are.
I... I...
I'm...
I'm a superhero.
Or... I wanna be.
That settles it.
You're Satoru.
Kayo's gonna die if I don't do something about it.
I know her mom's been hitting her,
and I swear I'm gonna put an end to it.
Lemme get this straight.
You think if you save her,
it will make you a superhero?
Well, if you ask me,
that makes you one already.
And I wanna be one, too.
So let me help.
Whaddya say?
I always heard opposites attract,
so I didn't think you'd like Kayo.
I mean,
you're kind of the same.
I didn't like her at first, but... I don't know.
There's something about her.
Huh.
I think I get what you mean.
Kenya, Satoru.
You're the bucket brigade.
Superheroes always get the shaft, don't they?
Damn straight.
Oh, I just remembered.
I have to check on something.
Can I meet you guys at the Children's Center?
‐Mm‐hmm.
‐Sure.
Tomorrow's March 1st.
As long as Kayo's not alone at the park, she'll be safe.
The problem's March 2nd, though,
the day of our birthday party.
I wanna give Yuuki an alibi.
Hey, Yuuki, is your dad's
bedroom on the first floor?
Uh... yeah.
His room faces the street.
What's up?
Oh, nothing.
I bet it gets noisy at night, though.
N‐No, not really.
Good.
One last thing to check.
Yuuki, you ever play with Kayo?
Wh‐Why?
It's just, she hangs with me and my friends now.
Oh, yeah?
So that's why I haven't seen her around lately.
Yes! Awesome!
That's the best goddamn thing for her.
That's the first time I ever heard
him use a cussword around me.
T‐Take care. See you around.
Yeah, bye.
The killer must have seen Yuuki with Kayo.
That's why he picked him to take the fall for her murder.
Don’t worry, Yuuki.
This time I'll stop it from happening.
Kayo, Kenya?
Hiromi?
- I'm open.
- No way, dude!
‐ Pass it! -Over here!
‐ Hey, about time.
‐ Wanna shoot some hoops?
‐ Yeah, come on. Three‐on‐three.
There was only me and her here last time.
I know what's gonna happen
between now and March 2nd,
but if things change too much,
I won't.
I gotta be careful about that.
I'm home!
Ready and...
Kayo, Satoru.
‐Happy birthday!
‐Happy birthday, guys!
March 1st was Day X
and everything happened the same as last time.
It's safe to start changing the future now.
Darn it.
I left something at school.
‐ Can't it wait till tomorrow? We have company!
‐We'll save a slice for ya.
It's weird bailing on the party,
but I can't worry about it.
‐Here we go!
‐
What in the hell? Hey, who's there?!
That takes care of that.
The cops are gonna be the perfect alibi for Yuuki.
Now for her.
I know how I can keep her away from Kayo.
One push. Just one push!
I know what you're thinking,
but don't.
What if the fall kills her?
You don't want that.
You'd get caught and then you can't help anyone.
Satoru, I wasn't just passing by, I've been following you.
The past few days, you've been so desperate to save Kayo.
I was worried you'd do something drastic.
I'm sorry about that.
It's just...
I knew tonight was when she was
gonna be in the most danger.
Earlier, I watched you huck a big
old rock through someone's window.
Why did you do that?
Oh. Yeah, that.
I wanted the police there so I could help someone else.
Kenya,
I really need your help.
If we can get the police involved in this,
they'll stop Kayo's mom.
I don't know,
that could stir up all kinds of trouble.
That's what I'm hoping.
‐But there's a chance it will backfire on you.
‐I know.
It's just an idea.
I'm still working out the details.
I don't care what I do or if the police catch me.
Or if they lock me up for good.
I don't care what happens to me.
As long as Kayo's safe.
Well, just don't do anything that will get you arrested.
Your mom will kick your butt.
No she won't.
When she found out what I did,
she'd say, "Nice job, kiddo."
Yeah, I guess she would.
All right, what's next?
- ‐ I'm gonna walk Kayo home.
-  ‐ Sure, go for it.
Yeah, we can handle the cleaning up.
This time I remembered to put
on a jacket and some gloves.
‐Kayo...
‐Satoru...
Me first.
I was thinking,
can you let me kidnap you?
You're an idiot.
Yeah, but that's the best I could come up with.
OK.
I was hoping you would say that.
This is it.
Pretty cool, huh?
Izumi's Elementary's hockey club
used to use it as their hangout.
Hey, guys.
About time.
Are you sure this is OK?
Yeah.
The school got a new one last year.
They use this for storage now.
We should open the vents before lighting the stove.
It's all rusted.
I'll cover the windows, you hang the blanket.
OK.
- ‐Cool.
- ‐ Wow!
It's an awesome hideout,
isn't it?
I wouldn't mind living here myself.
You'd miss having a shower, though.
Living in a proper house doesn't guarantee happiness.
Anyway... I should get going.
See you later, Kayo.
I should go home now, too,
but I'll come back later.
I'll knock three times.
Thanks, you guys.
I mean it. Thank you.
We're friends. You don't have to thank me, ever.
We're gonna keep you safe,
Kayo, promise.
- ‐ Ow!
-  ‐ Way to pour on the charm.
Yeah?
You should talk.
You sounded like you were
gonna ask her out or something.
You know I wouldn't do that to you.
I'm glad she's my friend,
and I know she's glad she's yours.
Thanks for helping.
Like I told her,
you don't have to thank me.
Besides,
the hard part's coming up.
Yeah. Listen,
if this does backfire on me,
make like you didn't know anything,
OK?
OK.
I didn't think you were ever coming home.
Sorry.
We stopped along the way.
We got to talking about stuff.
Stuff, huh?
I think her mom was worried, too.
‐She didn't call here, did she?
‐Nope, she didn't.
Oh, I have to leave super early tomorrow,
but don't get up for me.
I'll have this for breakfast.
Mm‐hmm.
Come in.
Did I wake you?
No. I couldn't sleep.
I don't blame you.
You hungry?
It's good.
This stuff tastes better late at night, huh?
I never had them this late before.
Oh.
You know what?
Me and the guys are gonna go camping this summer.
If you want, you should come.
I don't know if I can.
Sure you can.
Mm‐hmm.
Wake up.
We're gonna be late.
Good thing I stopped by.
Come on, we have to leave before
the kids from Izumi show up.
Where is Kayo? Anyone know?
Just a reminder.
It's flu season, so don't forget
to wash your hands before lunch.
I thought something would have happened by now.
What do you think?
Has her mom called the police?
Does she even know she's gone?
Maybe she hasn't looked for her yet.
The last time,
it was March the 2nd.
I got Kayo home before 9:00.
After that, her mom and the boyfriend beat her.
Then her mom threw her in the shed,
and sometime after 10:00,
Kayo was kidnapped.
At 12:30 on the 3rd,
Kayo's mom called up my mom.
Then, sometime before dawn,
Kayo was murdered.
This time there have been major
changes to everyone's actions:
Kayo, her mom, us...
the killer.
Who knows what'll happen next?
Yes, this is Gaku Yashiro,
from Mikoto Elementary.
Sure. Yes, I'll hold.
Let's hear it!
- ‐ One! Two...
Just don't tell Kazu or Osamu.
Sorry for dragging you into this, Hiromi.
Oh, that's OK.
I'm just stoked you guys trusted me.
Besides, my folks won't get back till 8:00,
so this is better than sitting home alone.
You're a trouper, Kayo.
You must be super bored.
Hmm‐mm.
I haven't had this much fun in forever.
I'm glad I had the guts to do this.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll stop by your house.
Her mom won't have a choice
but to call the police then.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐Hey.
I get why we're doing what we're doing,
but what if we get in trouble?
Don’t worry about that.
I'll take the blame for what happens.
You're an idiot.
This whole thing is because of me,
and all you guys are doing is trying to help.
No one's gonna blame anyone for that.
And I win.
You're right.
Damn, she's smart.
On the way home, Kenya said,
"I bet you didn't think about that, huh?"
I said, "Nope," and then he said...
"In my book,
you are a superhero."
Is that... Satoru?