[Gaku] I'd like to tell you
a little story.
It happened a long time ago,
when I was in the sixth grade.
One day at school,
a girl brought a box
of hamsters to class.
And she was very upset.
She said she started with two,
and before she knew it,
they'd bred.
Now she had more
than she could take care of.
I happily took them for her.
When I got home that day,
I filled a big wine jug
with water.
Then I dropped the hamsters in
one by one.
When I checked on them
three hours later,
I couldn’t believe my eyes.
One hamster was still alive,
standing atop
the drowned corpse
of one of its siblings.
And I was thrilled.
I named it Spice and decided
to keep it for my pet.
Why? Because when I saw it
in the jug,
it reminded me of a story
called "The Spider's Thread."
Do you know it?
It's about a sinner in Hell
named Kandata
who, while alive,
once spared a spider's life.
Moved by this act
of compassion,
the Buddha lowered
a spider's thread from paradise
down to him.
Kandata started climbing it,
and half way up,
he saw his fellow sinners
climbing after him.
He tried to knock them off,
and then...
[snap!]
the thread snapped,
sending Kandata back down
to Hell.
Now, what I'm about
to tell you next
might sound hard to believe,
but if anyone could understand,
it would be you.
Ever since I met Spice,
I could see the spider's thread
on people.
Whomever it touched,
I was compelled to kill.
But then a boy came along
who disrupted my duties.
And wouldn't you know it,
I saw the spider's thread
attached to him.
Yashiro!
I know your future!
[Gaku] I tried to kill
the boy, but he didn't die.
So I nicknamed him Spice,
and I kept a close eye on him.
[whispering] That boy
was you, Satoru!
[theme song plays]
[man singing in Japanese]
[Sachiko] That'll be
987 yen, please.
Thanks for shopping with us.
[Sachiko thinking]
Satoru mentioned something
to me once about the train.
[Satoru] Remember, you don't
have to change trains
to go to Ueno.
[Sachiko thinking]
He was right.
But why did he
point that out to me?
Good morning, kiddo.
Sleep well?
[projector clicks on]
[doctor] Huh.
He's in great shape
for someone who's been
in a coma for 15 years.
‐[Sachiko gasps]
‐[Satoru faintly] Fifteen years.
Wow! Talking already.
It won't be long before you can
start physical therapy.
[young Satoru] I heard that
for the past 15 years,
mom spent four hours a day
giving every joint
in my body a workout.
About three years ago,
she got one of those
EMS monitor thingies
to let her know
when I was conscious again.
She got another thing
to stimulate my muscles.
When I was in fifth grade,
I stood about 4½ feet tall.
I'm 5'5" now.
Dr. Kitamura said,
if it wasn't for my mom,
I wouldn't be in
as good a shape as I am.
[doctor] This might be difficult
but I think you're ready for it.
Try to answer my next question.
What's the last thing
you can remember,
before you lost consciousness,
that is?
[Satoru] OK.
I remember I was...
[young Satoru] Oh...
Wait.
Damn it.
[young Satoru]
It's like these memories,
whatever they are,
are locked behind a door.
[doctor] That's you.
‐Well, aren't you surprised?
‐Hmm?
Your face has changed a lot.
The last time you saw it,
you were 11.
Well, I guess since
your memories are scrambled,
it'll take a while
before this all sinks in.
It's just a matter of time.
[young Satoru] That day,
I thought maybe the doc
was right.
I should have felt weird
waking up in this time.
But I didn't.
But the thing is,
I should have.
Patience, heart rate monitor,
sense of loss, arbitration.
I knew those words.
But when did I learn them?
What the heck happened to me?
[door creaking]
[Sachiko] Good morning, Satoru.
Good morning, Mom.
[Sachiko] Guess what?
You've got some visitors.
Look who decided
to wake up.
You look great.
How are you feeling?
[young Satoru] I remember
Kenya and Hiromi.
They were two
of my very best friends.
Kenya's a lawyer now
and Hiromi's a doctor.
We talked for hours
about this and that.
Now and then I got the feeling
Kenya wanted to ask me
something, but he didn't.
Maybe Mom told him not to.
We just talked
about trivial things.
‐See ya later.
‐Take it easy.
[young Satoru] There was
lots of stuff I wanted
to ask the guys.
But Mom being Mom, I bet
she wanted to avoid that
to spare me from the shock.
For 15 years, she dedicated
herself to keeping me alive,
hoping I'd wake up one day.
She doesn't want me
to remember what happened.
It's probably
a good thing I don't.
[Satoru straining]
[nurse] I got ya.
We'll try it again tomorrow, OK?
[woman] Satoru?
Congratulations, Kayo.
[Kayo] Yeah, I'm married.
My last name is Sugita.
No way.
So Hiromi's a dad now?
‐[Kayo] Mm‐hmm.
‐I got the feeling
he wanted to tell me
something important:
now I know what.
He looks just like him.
He's even got the same
long eyelashes.
Yep. He's just like his daddy.
We named him Mirai.
That's a cool name.
It means "the future."
[Kayo] You know, we felt weird
about getting together.
It didn't seem right
for us to be happy.
We're alive because
of what you did
and because of us,
you ended up in a coma.
It felt like...
like we were leaving you
behind, I guess.
Kayo, whatever happened
to me happened.
So don't go blaming yourself
about it.
I don't have any regrets,
'cause in the end,
I'm here 'cause it's where
I'm supposed to be.
After being gone for 15 years,
you're still a smooth talker.
Oh, I am?
I get what you're saying,
Satoru,
but before you came along,
I thought I'd always be
alone in life.
And here I am
with my very own family.
You made that possible,
so thank you.
[young Satoru] She said...
"thank you."
But I can't remember what for.
[baby crying]
Uh‐oh, someone's hungry.
OK, OK.
[crying]
Satoru, are you OK?
[Satoru, weakly] Yeah.
I shouldn’t have
sprung all this on you.
It's a lot to process.
Well, we'll see you later.
Yeah, see you later.
[door opens]
Hey, kiddo,
you have a good workout today?
Uh‐huh. Kayo came by
a little while ago.
[Sachiko] Mm.
I bumped into her outside.
She's got the cutest baby.
[Satoru] Listen, Mom?
What's up?
‐Not those assholes again.
‐What?
[Sachiko] Paparazzi
from the gossip rags
looking for a story.
Waking up after 15 years
made you a celebrity.
‐Oh.
‐Screw 'em.
[Sachiko] Anyway, you wanted
to tell me something?
No. It wasn't important.
‐[knock on door]
‐[Sachiko] Come in.
‐How are we doing?
‐[Sachiko] So far, so good, doc.
[Satoru] I was wondering...
when do you think I'll
be able to walk again?
[doctor] I don't know.
It depends on you.
[Satoru] If it's OK, I'd like
to do twice as much rehab.
‐Why?
‐I wanna walk outside again.
‐Uh, sure, I'll see
what I can do.
‐[phone vibrating]
Sorry, I have to take this.
Yes, Director. Yes, sir.
He's doing great, actually.
He should get all his memoires
back any time now.
I'm sorry, no.
Like I told you the other day,
I'm not comfortable with that.
With all due respect,
he's my patient,
not a guinea pig...
I have to go.
[straining]
[nurse] You're doing great,
Satoru.
Your arms and legs
have gotten a lot stronger.
‐[nurse 1] Congratulations.
‐[nurse 2] Way to go!
[nurse 2] You walked
the whole way without our help.
[nurse 1] Awesome job!
‐[door opens]
‐[Sachiko] Hey, Satoru, Kenya
stopped by for a little visit.
[Satoru] Hi, Kenya.
[Kenya] I hope it's OK
I stopped by.
Are you kidding?
Of course it is.
[Sawada] Hello, Satoru.
Have we met before?
[Sawada] Matter of fact,
we have.
Your mom and I used
to work together
‐back before you started
elementary school.
‐[Satoru] Oh.
Come on, you honestly
think he'd remember you?
That was like 20 years ago now.
[Kenya] All right,
take care, buddy.
[Sawada] See you later.
We've waited 15 years.
No reason to get impatient.
‐We should go easy on him.
‐[Kenya] Yeah.
[Satoru] Hi, Kumi.
Ah, so the surgery's
in two weeks, huh?
They're gonna put some of my
big sister's bone marrow in me.
They said it will cure me.
But even so, I'm scared.
[Kumi]
You were asleep for 15 years?!
I know you've been
at this hospital for a while.
‐What's it been,
like three months now?
‐Mm‐hmm.
It's gonna be hard to stay
motivated in physical therapy
once you leave.
You’re the reason
I was working so hard.
Courage...
Whenever I need courage,
here's what I do.
I picture someone
I really care about smiling.
It only works
if I smile back, though.
[man] "The time‐traveling pedo.
He wakes up an adult,
but he's still a kid at heart.
Still hot for little girls.
Soon he'll be released.
Hide your children."
‐What do you think?
‐Good angle.
[Gaku] Taking photos
of a civilian without
their permission.
Slander, trespassing.
If I see you again,
I'll call the police.
Get out of here. Now.
They were some of the prettiest
flowers I'd ever seen.
Oh, hello, Mr. Nishizono.
Hello, Kumi.
‐Satoru Fujinuma.
‐Uh... yes?
It's me. Don't you remember?
It's OK. I've changed a lot
since the last time you saw me.
I was your homeroom
teacher once,
when you were in fifth grade.
I'm Gaku Yashiro.
I go by Manabu Nishizono now.
I changed my name
a while back.
Why did you change it,
if you don't mind me asking?
[Manabu] Not at all.
I got married five years ago
‐and took on my wife's
family's name.
‐[Satoru] Oh.
[Manabu] My father‐in‐law
was a city council member
for a long time.
But he passed away
three years ago.
I joined the council and took
over his constituency.
I kept the kanji
for my given name,
but I use
the more common reading now.
Wow. A real‐life politician.
[Manabu] Just a lowly
council member.
Yeah, well, still,
I get the feeling
you'd be super awesome
at politics, Mr. Yashiro.
[Manabu chuckles]
[Manabu] Anyway, I met
Kumi and her parents
at a charity event
for kids with leukemia.
I know the director
of this hospital,
so I pulled some strings
and got her in.
[Satoru] That's nice of you.
[Manabu] When I heard you
came to, I wanted to come visit.
I'm sorry it took me so long,
but with work and all.
[Satoru] Well, thanks
for taking the time.
[Manabu] To be honest,
I've been looking forward
to this day
for the past 15 years.
Yeah, well, me too.
[Manabu] You don't remember
how close we were, do you?
I don't. Sorry.
No, it's all right.
They said it would
take a while before
you got your memories back.
You'll remember me, in time.
♪
[Manabu] Hello.
‐[Satoru] Mr. Yashiro.
‐Were you on your way
to see Kumi?
Yeah. Her surgery's coming up.
The nurses said today
is the last day
she can have visitors.
[Manabu] True.
I just left her room.
She was asleep, so unfortunately
I couldn't talk to her.
Well, that sucks.
I guess I'll try
seeing her later, then.
Uh... since you're here,
can I talk to you?
[Manabu] Sure, but let's go
someplace we can have
some privacy,
away from these reporters.
Don't worry,
I know the perfect spot.
OK, here we are.
I'll bet you didn't know
about this elevator.
Feels like we're going
on an adventure, huh?
Would you push
the button for the roof?
[finger tapping]
Hmm. Too bad.
The sunset
would have been amazing
if it weren't raining.
At least we won't be bothered
by any paparazzi up here.
But the roof's off‐limits
so don't tell on me, OK?
It's funny,
being up here reminds me
of how you, Kenya and Hiromi
always talked about going
to your hideout after school.
[Satoru] Yashiro...
I remember everything,
you son of a bitch.
[theme song plays]
[woman singing in Japanese]