Kayo's late. Again.
But she said she was gonna
give me my present today.
Maybe she was up all night
making it and overslept.
‐ Satoru?
‐Yeah.
‐Satoru?
‐Huh? Yes, sir!
Everything all right,
or is there something on your mind?
Kayo?!
Open up, it's me!
Kayo!
Oh, no.
Rubber boot tracks.
Too big to be a kid's.
It snowed two nights ago.
And these tracks are fresh.
Whoever was here was an adult.
Probably male.
Shit.
Now what do we do?
I didn't go back to school
for two days.
Huh. I guess Mom went
to the store.
I found out a kid got snatched not
too long ago over in the next town.
But the cops already caught
that scumbag.
This guy is someone new.
We have to warn people before he does it again.
The problem is the police put a gag order on the story.
What about airing it when kids aren't watching?
The station could do that easy.
And I can go talk to the school
and see if they'll issue a warning.
‐ OK. I'll talk to the boss about your idea.
‐ I'd appreciate it.
He's a reporter for Ishikari TV.
My Mom used to work with him.
The last thing I want is for Satoru to
grow up with horrible memories like this.
I hear you.
Making me forget was her idea.
I know you're worried,
but you gotta eat something.
What happened
isn't your fault, kiddo.
I tried
but I couldn't help her.
I don't know about that.
I just... I didn't
want her to be alone.
And thanks to you,
she wasn't.
It wasn't enough.
I should have done more.
Look, what happened happened.
So it's pointless to beat
yourself up about it.
In a situation like hers,
there’s only so much anyone could have done.
That goes for you and me.
You should go back to school tomorrow.
- ‐You'll just feel worse staying here alone.
-  ‐ OK.
Good. Now eat up, OK?
Yeah.
I, uh,
have a confession.
The other day, I told you Kayo was
home with a cold. That's not true.
She's staying with her grandmother
in Sapporo for personal reasons.
It happened so fast,
she didn't have a chance to say goodbye.
But don’t worry,
I hear she's doing well.
She ran away.
I heard Kayo's mom
hit her with a broom.
Oh, my God, really?
It's better
she's with her grandma.
Hey, Satoru.
‐Cheer up, man.
‐Yeah, don't worry.
‐You'll see her again.
‐Mm‐hmm.
Satoru, the school and the PTA talked
about it and decided this was for the best.
I hate to ask this, but could
you go along with the story?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
The press couldn't
talk about it either.
And for the past few days,
the police had a car parked outside Kayo's house.
They were watching it because they
pegged her mom as the prime suspect.
Then, six days
after Kayo disappeared...
Listen up, everyone,
I have an announcement.
From now on, when you leave school,
make sure you're either with your parents...
...the next girl was kidnapped,
sooner than
she should have been.
You hear
about Aya Nakanishi?
I don't know if you knew her,
but she was a student at Izumi Elementary.
I heard.
I have a friend who goes there and he said
she ran away to go live with her grandfather.
She did, huh?
Just like Kayo.
She didn't run away.
That’s a lie.
If you ask me, there's
a kidnapper on the loose.
The details might not be
exactly the same,
but things were definitely following
the same flow of time as before.
Stations ran stories on the missing girls all
day, except Ishikari TV.
They only ran them early in
the morning and late at night.
So parents were advised to have
their kids watch Ishikari TV only.
‐
‐ I'm home.
After Aya Nakanishi went
missing, I noticed something.
The cops had dialed back
their stakeout at Kayo's place.
They must have realized a serial
kidnapper was on the loose.
Ten days after Kayo disappeared...
I saw her mom toss out
a bag of trash.
A pair of mittens was in it.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
Promise.
Where am I?
‐I'm back in 2006 again.
‐
Address: 23‐1 Fourth Street.
Victim: Sachiko Fujinuma.
Female, 52.
Suspect is her son,
Satoru Fujinuma, 29.
We're talking
to the eyewitness now.
Over.
‐
‐ Are you Satoru Fujinuma?
No, it wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
Goddamn it.
I couldn't save Kayo.
Mom's still dead.
Everyone still thinks I killed her.
I couldn't change anything after all.
Only one thing to do.
Run.
I'm hiding under a bridge in a box.
Talk about clichés.
I wonder if I made the news yet.
Come on, think.
Why was Mom murdered?
Did she know who the killer was?
When I found her, I didn't see
her phone anywhere.
Or her bag.
They were both gone.
The killer took 'em, but why?
I bet she had evidence on him,
and he was scared the cops would find it.
Shit.
I'm crashing hard.
If I only had a day to sleep,
I'd think better.
‐ There you go.Eat up.
‐ Thanks.
I'm sorry about work today.
It's no big deal.
One no‐show won't get you fired.
Airi was worried about you, though.
I wasn't 'cause I figured you
had a pretty good reason.
We can talk about it after we eat.
Thanks.
That sucks. Fight with your mom
was that bad, huh?
‐Yeah.
‐That's the trouble with old folks.
They can be hella stubborn.
You can crash here as long as you want.
But your mom's your mom,
so try and patch things up with her.
I will.
Hey,
you want a beer?
- ‐ No.
- ‐ Crap, I'm all out.
I'm gonna go out
and get some more.
He's kind of a knob,
but his heart's in the right place.
I feel bad for lying.
Police rushed to the apartment
after receiving an anonymous tip.
Inside, they found the body of a woman
believed to be the tenant's mother.
The suspect, described as
a male in his late 20s,
fled the scene
before he could be questioned.
The police are currently searching
the neighborhood for him.
This is not good.
This is so not good.
And now the sports minute.
Japan's soccer team is heading
for the playoffs in Germany today
for what some are calling the most...
Should have known he'd screw me over.
What am I saying? I can't blame him.
He was just trying to do the right thing.
If I was in his shoes, I'd do the same.
Goddamn it.
Uggh!
‐
‐ You're an idiot.
Airi?
No way! You called me by my first name?
That's a first.
You know, if you're on the run,
you shouldn't leave your phone on.
The police can use GPS
to track you.
Oh.
Are you just gonna sit there?
Hop on, let's go.
Come on, shake a leg.
Sorry about this, Katagiri.
Call me Airi.
It's one of the perks
of riding tandem.
I can't believe
you let me in your house.
You do know why
they're after me, right?
The cops came to see
the manager today.
I overheard them
talking about it.
‐It was on the news, too.
‐Then why did you risk helping me get away?
'Cause you didn't kill her, that's why.
At dinner, I could see how much you
guys meant to each other. That's a fact.
Yeah, well...
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
I can't imagine what you're going through,
and to have the cops after you, too?
You don't deserve that.
No one deserves the kind of stuff
you've been through before, either.
What?
This. You left it behind
at work the other day.
One of the chapters had a stickie
so I went ahead and read it.
Talked all about what happened in
your hometown when you were a kid,
how Kayo Hinazuki was murdered.
I cried when I read it.
She died the day of the Girls Festival.
It says that?
Yeah. It says she died
on March 3rd.
Anyway, make yourself at home.
I have to take the bike back
before they miss it.
And don't even think
about leaving this room.
This isn't
how it was before.
It changed.
I changed it.
If I can go back again,
I can save Kayo.
Oh, yeah, I'm in Airi's room.
"Dear Satoru,
I think I should stick
to my normal schedule today,
so I'm going in to work
my usual shift.
The fam said they'd be
leaving the house around 10
and won't be coming back
till after 8 tonight.
The key to the house and my
bike are next to my clock.
Here's the number to my cell.
Wait.
I thought her last name was Katagiri.
Thank you,
Mr. Nishizono!
I can't tell you how much
we appreciate it.
Well, your father's done so much for
me, I wish I could do more.
Oh, God, no, believe me,
you've done enough.
Heck, my dad couldn't be happier.
Thanks to that stoplight
and crosswalk you approved,
we get more customers now
than ever before.
Please.
Your business is doing well
because your father is
a shrewd businessman.
All I did was give him
a little boost, that's all.
Besides, it's a school route.
Safety first, you know.
The city council's been talking about
putting a stoplight here for ages.
I left the receipts by the till.
Heading home.
Sure. Nice hustle today, Airi.
- ‐What you got there?
-  ‐ Oh, just some leftover pizza.
Leftovers, are you kidding?
Go on, get a fresh one. My treat.
Thanks for the offer, boss,
but this will do.
My friend won't know the difference anyway.
Oh,
uh, I hope she likes it, then.
That is, if your friend's a, you know, girl.
Yeah, well...
see you tomorrow.
She’s a cute girl, huh?
Yeah, I guess,
if you're into that sort of thing.
I mean she's 17.
She's just a kid.
Yeah, well... I should
get back to the office.
Thanks for stopping by, sir.
Hey, Airi!
‐What's up?
‐Here. You forgot to take this.
It is part of the promotion
after all.
Oh. OK, thanks.
I was wondering, have you talked
to Satoru lately?
‐No.
‐I can't believe he'd just up and kill his own...
I mean, you know
what they're saying he did.
‐It's not like the guy at all.
‐No, it isn't.
I don't know how tight you guys were,but if you see him,
do what you can to help him, OK?
Sure.
Let him know we're on his side.
And if you talk to him, give me a shout.
Yeah, I totally will.
What am I doing?
I doubt I'm gonna find
anything.
A kid disappeared here.
Three years ago.
Yeah, I think I remember this.
And three weeks later,
they arrested some guy for it.
Even after the trial,
he swore he was innocent.
It's a hell of a coincidence.
Or... is it?
Why would you wanna go
and call the police for?
Airi!
Is that why you wanted me
to help Satoru?
You said you were on his side.
You said that!
Wait a sec, Airi.
I just...
I was worried about you,
that's all.
If all you wanted was to get him caught,
you should have told me the truth!
I trusted you!
I trusted you and you lied to me!
I didn't want to see you get hurt,
I swear.
‐ That I believe.
‐I'm sorry.
Boss, please...
If you're really worried about me,
then don't call the police over here.
I don't want my family
getting involved in this.
I'm sorry, Satoru.
Nah, it's no big deal.
I got to sleep a bit,
so thanks for letting me stay
and conk out on your floor.
No, don't mention it.
I just wish you could go back.
It's OK.
It's better if I don't.
By the way, that's not
your parents' house, is it?
Huh‐uh. I'm staying
with my uncle and his wife.
My town doesn't have a high school.
It's out in the boonies,
so I had to come to the city for it.
I asked my uncle and he said
I could stay with them in Chiba.
- ‐ Mind if I ask a weird question?
-  ‐ Hmm‐mm.
Like, why do you believe me?
You don't even know me all that well.
You're right, I don't,
but I don't care.
I want to believe you.
When I was
in elementary school,
my dad took me
grocery shopping one day.
The owner stopped my dad and
accused him of stealing a candy bar.
Like I said, my town's small,
so the owner knew my dad.
He said if he just admitted stealing
it, he'd drop the whole thing.
But he refused, and the owner
kept pushing him.
I never heard my dad yell before,
but that day he went off.
The owner ended up calling the police.
And since my dad belonged
to the local farmers' co‐op,
they gave him a three‐month
suspension as punishment.
You didn't steal it, Daddy.
I know! I saw, you didn't do anything wrong!
After what happened,
Dad quit the co‐op,
divorced Mom, and left.
I guess my Mom thought
he really stole it.
Like everyone else in town.
If someone believes in you,
you're not alone.
And if I was in your situation,
I'd want someone to believe me.
I think you should go home.
Tell the cops I forced you to hide me.
They'll buy that story.
God, you're an idiot.
You can't deal with this on your own.
And I won't lie to the police.
- ‐OK, but could you not call me an idiot anymore?
-  ‐
No promises!
I'll be back in a sec with a change
of clothes and stuff for you.
The boss didn't call the police after all.
Good for him.
But...
it can't be.
What is this?
It can't be from him 'cause he
told me his mom's phone was gone.
Unless he found it.
No, it's from the killer.
He's after me now.
Oh, my God!
Gotta get out!
I gotta...