I get what you're saying,
but before you came along,
I thought I'd always
be alone in life.
And here I am
with my very own family.
You made that possible.
So thank you.
[young Satoru]
She said "thank you."
but I can't remember
what for.
[baby crying]
Uh‐oh, someone’s hungry.
OK, OK.
[young Satoru]
I remember now!
I saved Kayo's life.
After that, I made sure
Misato and Aya
were never alone,
to keep them safe
from the kidnapper.
And then...
[Satoru] Yashiro...
I remember everything,
you son of a bitch!
[theme song plays]
[man singing in Japanese]
[Satoru] No way.
Kazu's a carpenter?
He and Osamu look like
they're doing great.
[Hiromi] Mm‐hmm.
By the way, Misato said she was
going to come by and see you.
What? Really?
I thought she hated my guts
after what happened in class.
Yeah, I remember that.
The lunch money thing she pulled
was so messed up.
It was, but don't forget
who started raising funds
to help pay
Satoru's medical bills.
She did that, too.
I had no idea.
[Kenya] Tell us about
the day you tailed her.
You know,
when you saw the killer.
Knew it.
You do remember everything.
But then
why didn't you tell us?
I didn't want
to get you involved.
It's been 15 years.
Whatever evidence there was
is gone by now.
And besides,
who'd believe me?
Like you said,
it's been 15 years.
Now that you're back,
I couldn't be happier,
because it's a miracle
you woke up at all.
That's why I didn't
bring it up before,
to spare you from the shock.
The last thing you need is
someone digging up the past
when you're trying to recover.
But you remember everything.
So, if you want to catch
the killer,
you don't have to do it alone.
Let us help you.
Hiromi's been coming here
to visit you all these years,
and now
he wants to be a doctor.
I became a lawyer,
and now I'm working with
Mr. Sawada to catch the killer.
Hiromi and I are who we are
because of you, Satoru.
You were a hero
to us back then.
and we want to help you again,
just like old times.
Just like we helped with Kayo.
You trusted me enough back then,
believed in me, you remember?
That's why I believed in you.
If someone believes in you,
you're not alone.
And if I was in
your situation,
I'd want someone
to believe me.
[Satoru thinking] Airi.
I'm not alone.
I have friends
I can count on.
The killer is...
Yashiro.
[Yashiro] I knew you remembered.
On the way up here,
I tapped my finger on
your wheelchair a couple times.
I could tell you tried hard
not to react.
Fifteen years ago,
you figured out what I was doing
and ruined my plans.
But how?
A child isn't capable
of such tings.
It's as if you were
psychic or something.
[young Satoru] Yashiro!
I know your future!
Let's have it.
How did you know
what I was thinking?
What did you mean,
you know my future?
What difference does it make?
Soon as I tell you,
you'll kill me.
[Yashiro] Oh, I know
what you're up to.
You’ve got a phone
in your pocket.
Are you recording us?
Or is someone listening in?
Kenya, perhaps?
You have heard of
the statute of limitations?
Even if I confessed, I can't be
tried for things I did
15 years ago.
And I haven't done
anything wrong since then.
So you see,
no matter what you do,
you can never get me, Satoru.
Oh, look, Kumi just
sent you an email.
At 4:30, she'll get
her daily IV.
I put a muscle relaxant
in her dose
and made sure your fingerprints
were all over the bag.
That poor little girl who was
afraid of her operation
will die peacefully now
thanks to you.
And feeling guilty,
I throw myself off the roof,
isn't that right?
There you go
reading my mind again.
While that might be
an amazing skill,
it won't save your life.
But you might save Kumi's if
you tell me what I want to know.
If I do, then what?
How do I know you won't
kill her anyway?
I can't guarantee I won't,
naturally.
But there is a possibility.
If you don't talk,
there won't even be that.
I hate to say it.
We're out of time now.
There was a 50‐50 chance
you'd tell me
how you knew about me back then.
Oh, well, I guess
it doesn't matter anymore.
I'm sure it was just
a coincidence
when you screamed
you knew my future.
That was just a bluff.
As for your mother...
we should send her an email,
let her know how sorry you are.
[Sachiko] Hey, kiddo,
I have to work
the morning shift tomorrow,
so I'll see you
in the afternoon?
I'll let him sleep.
[Satoru, weakly] Mom?
I lied to you.
I got my‐‐
Your memory back?
I know.
It happened when Kayo came by.
[Satoru thinking]
Yep, she's a witch.
You're right, but how come
you didn't tell her
not to bring up the past?
[Sachiko sighs]
[Sachiko] After Kenya
and Hiromi stopped by,
I felt I made a mistake
telling them not to bring
any of it up.
They couldn't say
what they wanted,
and that wasn't fair.
When Kayo showed up
with her baby,
I didn't have the heart
to ask her to do the same.
After waiting all this time
for you to wake up,
who am I to stop her?
I got to see your face
and talk to you every day
for the last 15 years.
Then when I heard you speak,
your voice all crackly,
it finally hit me,
you weren't a kid anymore.
I was happy...
My boy grew up.
Mom, I'm gonna
take life head‐on.
What in the heck
are you talking about?
Even when you were a little kid,
you always took it head‐on,
remember?
Mm‐hmm.
[Satoru] Life is about
filling up the void in yourself.
[Yashiro] Indeed.
Whenever I taught sixth grade,
I always told the class that.
I remember what your face
looked like.
The day they took Kayo
from her mom.
The expression you had
stuck with me
even after all these years.
A little while after I was born,
my dad took off.
So I have no idea
what he looks like.
But that day at Kayo's,
you were the dad I never had
and I always wanted.
At that moment,
you filled the void in me.
[Yashiro] For the last 15 years,
I've been waiting for you
to wake up.
When you slipped into your coma,
I lost the impulse
that defined me,
the thing
that gave my life meaning.
I've waited a long time.
But now...
You're not alone anymore?
So, how are we
gonna settle this?
Are you gonna turn yourself in
or kill me?
Which is it?
It's already settled, actually.
You're right, I beat you.
I saved all of them from you.
Kayo, Aya, Hiromi, Yuuki.
Even my mom,
who you haven't killed yet.
Your mom?
Why would I kill...
Hold on, are you saying
you can‐‐
[Satoru] I'm just telling you
what you wanted to know.
I could screw up all your plans
because I knew your future.
That's it.
That's how I saved them all.
That's why you weren't able
to kill anyone I was even
remotely connected to.
Why you couldn't kill me.
Wrong.
I could have killed you
anytime I wanted.
Now, for instance.
But for 15 years,
you let me live.
Why did you do that?
Oh, I know,
you needed me, didn't you?
I was your reason for living.
I was your hope.
I was the one who filled
the void in you.
I beat you back then,
Mr. Yashiro...
[Yashiro] No! No! No!
[Satoru] Even now, I beat you!
[Yashiro straining]
You see what I mean?
You can't kill me.
Fifteen years is a long time.
I was asleep, so for me
it all went by in a flash,
but for you,
it must have felt like forever.
You're still alive
'cause I'm around.
I make you feel alive.
I had to relive a part of
my life over and over again,
the part where you killed
some of my friends.
Funny, I should hate you,
but I don't.
'Cause right now, I'm
the only one who knows you.
The real you.
You're right.
Satoru.
I can't live...
[crash!]
You're right.
I can't go on living
without you.
[laughing]
[chuckles]
[Kenya] The police are charging
him with attempted murder.
[Satoru] Is Kumi OK?
[Kenya] Yeah, but I didn't
tell her about him,
what with her surgery
coming up and all.
[Satoru] Good.
"I believe in you."
What a strange thing to say.
‐Huh?
‐[Satoru] Well, think about it.
[Satoru] If you really believe
in someone, chances are,
they already know you do.
Saying it's kind of redundant,
don't you think?
[Kenya] Not if you mean it,
and you want someone
to know you do.
[Satoru] Yeah.
I guess we say it
'cause we want
to give someone hope.
Hope to keep fighting.
To let them know they're not
alone in the world, right?
[Satoru] Now my life
has a blank spot
between the ages of 11
and 25.
But in a weird way, I sort of
treasure the time I lost.
In a town without me,
my friends lived for themselves
and for me.
‐[indistinct chatter]
‐[Hiromi] Where is he?
[Kazu] Heroes always show up
at the last minute.
‐Right?
‐Here's Satoru.
‐About time.
‐Where you been?
‐What's up, dude?
‐You're an idiot.
Are you ever on time?
[young Satoru]
A town without me.
Time without me.
It's not my loss,
it's my treasure.
Whoa!
This is great!
Whenever you dig deep,
you always come up
with the most amazing angles.
Thanks. I guess I'll keep
working on it, then.
That‐a‐boy.
And sorry you had to
schlep out here.
So, you heading out today?
Yep. Going back to Hokkaido
for a break.
There's some old friends
I wanna see.
Well, have yourself
a great time, then.
Safe travels
and have a good weekend.
Oh, almost forgot.
Congrats on your anime
getting the green light.
[Satoru] I write and draw manga
for a living now.
As for Revival,
I haven't had another.
[woman singing in Japanese]
♪
[woman on radio]
The 2010 Olympics in Vancouver
are just two short weeks away.
The athletes representing Japan
are already...
‐I'm gonna go out for a walk.
‐We'll hold the fort down.
Later, boss.
Oh, I heard we'll be getting
some more snow later on,
so take a jacket...
[Satoru] "My Hero,"
by Satoru Fujinuma.
"I'm not brave enough
to make the first move...
[young Satoru] That's why
I don't have any real friends.
I play with other kids,
but there's a difference
between playing with them
and real friends.
Yesterday, I saw
the last episode of
'Fight, Wonder Guy!',
my favorite anime.
In the first part of it,
Wonder Guy had to fight
the bad guys by himself.
They'd knock him down
again and again,
but he had the courage
to get back up.
He'd say, "If I don't try,
nothing will change,"
and he'd jump
right back into the fight.
Other people saw
how courageous he was
and slowly but surely,
they joined him
and became his friends.
When it looked like
the bad guy
was gonna finish him off
for good, he didn't worry.
He never stopped believing
that his friends would come
to the rescue.
But someone like me doesn't
have Wonder Guy's courage
or real friends.
To be honest,
I feel kind of jealous.
I want friends
like his someday.
Real friends, the kind that
have my back no matter what."
Can you believe this snow?
The Weather Channel said
it's the most snow Kanto's
gotten in ten years! Ten!
Mind if I hang out here
with you till it stops?
[grown‐up Satoru] I never
stopped believing either.