I'm having a birthday party and I want you to come.
Uh...
You seem like you're OK. It's easy talking to you.
Well...
It's 'cause I decided to be honest with you.
I said that out loud.
Wait, Kayo!
So, um, see ya tomorrow?
Eighteen years ago, I saw Kayo here, alone.
And then she disappeared.
They found her body after the snow melted.
I remember she got kidnapped in March.
But what day was it?
That's what I have to figure out now.
Aya Nakanishi, Hiromi Sugita.
That's right, Hiromi.
Kayo was the only one who was 10.
That means she was kidnapped before her birthday.
That's it!
The day I'm looking for is between
March 1st and Kayo's birthday.
Day X.
Whoa! Ow!
Did you guys hear? The boys are gonna race one‐on‐one.
‐ Big deal. ‐ Why? What's the matter?
Why can't the girls...?
I betcha Hamada's gonna get the fastest time again.
Maybe.
Hamada! You're the awesomest‐est!
God, shut up.
‐ ‐Don't expect me to hold back.
No.
Hamada's on the school's hockey team.
They won the national championship.
Come to think of it, I did race him.
Satoru's gonna race Hamada next.
He doesn't stand a chance.
Well, Kayo, you gonna cheer your boyfriend on?
Yeah!
Come on, let's hear it.
Satoru, you got this?
Uh‐huh, I think so.
Good. You better not suck.
On your mark, guys.
Get set.
Crap!
Go! Faster!
What are you doing, Hamada?
Move it!
Damn, he's fast.
Satoru totally jumped the gun.
I can beat him, I can win.
But should I?
He's the one training like a fiend every day.
He deserves it.
I so totally knew he'd win!
That was rad!
He was so close, but he still kicked butt.
Right, Kenya?
You asshole.
What, you think you're doing me a favor?
I hate you!
Satoru.
That was super close.
Shut up!
What crawled up his butt?
He's probably just mad 'cause he almost lost.
It's cool.
I remember.
You think you're doing me a favor? I hate you!
Goddamn it.
I did the same thing 18 years ago.
Kayo, wait up!
Hamada was faster than I thought.
Yeah.
So, uh, what day is your birthday?
What's wrong?
Didn't you say you were gonna be honest with me?
I know, but I thought Hamada deserved to win more than me.
Oh.
Sorry.
It's fine.
After all, you and me are fakes and liars.
Satoru, wanna walk home?
I forgot something. I'll catch up!
Hey, what ya doing there?
Mr. Yashiro.
I, uh...
Is it about Kayo?
Whoa, he's sharp.
I wanted to know her birthday. Sorry, sir.
No worries.
By the way, I've noticed you two have gotten friendly.
I don't know about that.
Well, why didn't you just ask her?
I told her when mine is, but she wouldn't tell me hers.
Aha! I think I know why. Here, see for yourself.
What did he mean by that?
‐ ‐It's the same day as mine.
No way! Thanks a lot.
I have a feeling Kayo felt awkward about telling you.
She's a very shy girl, you know.
I wouldn't make too big a deal
out of it, know what I mean?
Mm‐hmm, you're right.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Satoru...
that was a close race.
Keep on doing your best, with Kayo too, OK?
OK.
Gaku Yashiro.
He's around my age here.
And as perceptive as I remember.
I know when Day X is.
March 1st.
Eleven days from now.
I have to make things right with Kayo.
Wh‐Where is she?
Hey, Satoru!
Yuuki!
It looks like you got yourself some friends, huh?
Good for you.
In this time, Yuuki's 23,
just a few years younger than I am.
It's 'cause of you, Yuuki.
Not even.
Y‐You just found the courage you always had in you.
Soon as folks saw how fun you were to be around,
it all f‐fell into place.
Same kind heart, same stutter.
He's a good guy.
Yuuki, do you know a girl named Kayo?
Little Kayo? Sure I know her.
That was quick.
I see her hanging out by herself in the park a lot.
I talked to her a bunch of times.
Is she in your class or something?
Yeah.
Oh, no way.
I didn't know that.
Yo, Jun, time to eat!
Thanks, Dad. I'll be there in a bit.
It's kind of early for dinner.
Yeah, but we get up early.
I start work at my dad's bento shop at 4 a. m.
Whoa, really!?
Mm‐hmm. I work from 4 to noon.
Oh.
I didn't think he had a job,
'cause every time we hung out, it was in the afternoon.
Now that I'm older, I think I get why he stuttered.
He was just nervous and trying to connect with me.
But to a kid, he came off as
really mature and kind of wise.
So, what kinds of stuff did you two talk about?
Did he ever make you feel nervous
or did you feel safe around him?
There's this neat article on a paper‐crafting tournament.
I forget which issue, though.
Um...
I'm just holding those for
someone so I can't throw them out.
No, it's cool, I don't care.
About his room. Did you see anything that made you uneasy?
Oh, it's late. I better go.
OK.
That's weird.
Somehow you seem more mature.
You think so?
Mm‐hmm.
Jun Shiratori.
In 2006, he's sitting on death row.
Ever since the first trial, he said he was innocent.
I can't believe he'd kill anyone, not Yuuki.
If the murders don't happen, he won't be a suspect.
Hang on, Yuuki, I'm gonna change everything.
I guess Kayo's not home yet.
Jeez, what a dump.
Hmm?
What's that?
Her gloves!
Oh, no!
Kayo!
Don't look.
Close the door.
What are you talking about? I'm getting you out of here!
Go away!
What ya doing in there, Kayo?
What do you keep coming out here by yourself for?
Bitch. You did this!
Come on, get up. Get in the house.
Wait! How did Kayo get those bruises?
Go on and answer him, honey.
I fell.
She was too scared to tell the truth.
And I was too shocked to say anything.
She kept walking and didn't look back.
Not even once.
Come on, let's get some of that swelling down.
You wanna show up for class on Monday with a puffy face?
No. 'Cause then they're gonna start asking me questions.
Hey! Don't waste the goddamn ice.
Where is she?
Morning, Satoru.
Good morning.
Morning.
Man, it's cold.
If you know the circumference,
divide it by 2 times 3.14 to find the radius.
If you know the diameter, just
divide it by two and that's the radius.
Now then, who...?
Thank God.
It's OK, go take your seat.
All right, which one of you wants
to come up and take a crack at this?
How about you, Satoru?
Aww, jeez!
Aww, come on.
You can do it.
Has everyone brought up their money?
I have to change the future.
Fast.
If you forgot it, please bring it tomorrow.
Yes, it is strange how Kayo's always
either tardy or absent on Mondays.
Do you have any idea why?
Yeah, I do. It's 'cause her mom beats her on Saturdays.
So, you've seen the bruises on her too, huh?
Wait, you knew about this?
I suspected.
Well, then why didn't you say anything?
I was worried what would happen if the students found out.
You see how the other kids avoid her.
If they found out she was being abused,
they'd tease her and make her life even more miserable.
They wouldn't do that!
I know you wouldn't. You're her friend.
That's why I'll tell you everything I know.
‐But keep it between us, OK? ‐Mm‐hmm.
I started to suspect Kayo's mother
was abusing her around last May.
I tried going through proper
channels, but it hasn't worked.
Why not?
Her mom's been cleverly avoiding the investigators.
Child Protective Services went to
her house three times to speak with her.
She must have known they were coming
because her and Kayo were never home,
so no official interview has happened yet.
What a bunch of useless people.
I said that out loud.
Yes, well, I've spoken with Kayo's mom a number of times.
There's no doubt she's abusing her daughter.
But I have to wait for CPS to confirm it.
When they do, they'll take Kayo away from her.
He's already got this figured out.
The thing is, once they intervene and get her to safety,
it means she won't be coming back here, ever.
I don't care about that as long as Kayo's safe.
The sooner, the better.
It's almost March,
so there's only a few days left to save her.
Someone has to do something now.
I have to do something.
Sit down, will ya?
Holy shit.
Where the hell's everyone's lunch money?
Oh, you'd think a 29‐year‐old would be
smart enough not to leave cash in his desk.
Mr. Yashiro?
What's up?
It's about the lunch money. I can't find it.
What? Huh? No! Figures.
Sir, I think I know what happened.
Someone must have stolen it.
And I have a feeling that someone is Kayo.
What? How do you know she did?
Who else could it be?
I mean, she doesn't have to
pay for her lunches like we do.
It sort of figures the thief would be someone who's poor.
Good point!
Did you take it, Kayo?
The brat!
The best way to find out who
stole it is to check everyone's bags.
She's right, teach. We should check 'em.
I just wanna eat my lunch.
This sucks. You gonna check your bag?
No. What's the point? I already
know I didn't take the cash.
Check the bag of the person next to you, too.
You stole it, didn't you?
Drop dead.
Hurry, find the thief!
I didn't find anything.
I bet it's Kayo.
I know, right?
Poorkid, schmoor kid!
Found it.
It was Kayo! The poor girl did it.
I told you she took it. Kayo's
a thief and should be expelled.
Shut up! It doesn't matter if she's poor or hungry!
Kayo would never steal anything from anyone!
I bet you took the money.
You know, anyone could have taken the cash
from Satoru's desk and planted in Kayo's bag.
All right, guys. Remember, Kayo was helping
collect the money earlier, so of course she'd have it.
Misato, Satoru, it's over. OK, everyone, back to lunch.
I knew she didn't do it.
Attention, students, classes are done for
the day and the school will be closing soon.
This isn't awkward.
Thanks for speaking up for me before.
Oh, sure. She had no right accusing you.
Back in third grade,
Misato made fun of my pencils,
so I took her favorite mechanical
pencil and chucked it out the window.
Since then, she's hated me like you wouldn't believe,
and I hated her right back.
This other time, she invited me
to a Christmas party at her house,
but that was only to show off how big her tree was.
It was really pretty, though.
I remember tonight.
Hey, after we're done here, wanna go see one?
One what?
A Christmas tree.
You're an idiot.
Here.
Hmm?
You're gonna need 'em.
It gets super cold up on the mountain.
I didn't say I was going to go with you.
I always used to come here to go skiing and bobsledding.
I'd even see a red fox or two.
There they are!
Aren't they cool?
I remembered the foxes running around and around.
But 18 years ago, I was by myself,
and no one believed me when I told them.
Were they a couple?
Mm‐hmm. I bet they were.
The sky's clearing up.
It's a perfect night.
There it is.
That's a Christmas tree!
Huh?
Don't be dumb, it's February.
We should come back in summer and see it.
Our Christmas tree.
You're an idiot.