Congratulations,
everyone.
In 1988, the first time I lived it,
Kayo Hinazuki and Aya Nakanishi disappeared
and their bodies were found later.
I was too helpless to save anyone.
I tried hard to forget, and I did.
But in the end, I had a big gaping hole in my heart.
These past six years,
we've experienced success and failure,
happiness and sadness.
Good or bad, the experiences we share
fill a void we all have inside of us.
Everyone. Even me.
So keep filling it,
and you'll enrich your life, and others' too.
That’s what life's about. Never forget that.
Uh, hey there.
Who are you?
- ‐ I'm Satoru Fujinuma.
- ‐ I'm Kenya Kobayashi.
‐ I'm Hiromi Sugita.
Have we met before?
Uh, you're Aya Nakanishi.
I heard you're good at piano.
Yeah, I guess.
So, did we meet in piano class?
Well, actually, no.
So, anyway, what you reading?
Oh, this? Shakespeare.
"King Lear." I've only read "Romeo and Juliet."
Reading this stuff and playing piano are my parents' idea.
I can't hear what they're talking about.
Maybe we should try and get a little closer.
Wait, now I remember where I've seen you before.
You're the kids who are always
sneaking into that old building.
Aren't you?
Darn it. So much for having a secret hideout.
Hideout? That's so childish.
‐ You...
‐You shouldn't call it childish.
Yeah, well, the only ones who sneak around building forts
and secret hideouts are little boys.
I bet you like playing superhero too.
Don't make fun of superheroes!
-Easy, Satoru!
-Nice meeting you, but I have to go now.
Bye, kids.
Hold up!
Kazu?!
‐What do you want?
‐A hideout...
is totally macho!
Uh...
You should come and see it sometime.
You'll get what I mean.
You're a bunch of weirdoes!
She’s childish.
You were so rad yesterday!
It's my gloves,
right where I left them 18 years ago.
‐Leveling up's a pain in the nuts.
‐That's what makes games fun.
Hey, Satoru,
Aya's gonna be at the park soon,
so maybe we should start heading over.
It's cool.
I can see the bench from here.
OK.
Yesterday was a wash.
I gotta figure out how to get close to her.
All right, I'm here to see this macho hideout of yours.
Um... thanks for coming, Aya.
Can you stay awhile?
Mm‐hmm.
- See you.
- Bye‐bye.
You off to see Aya again?
Yep. We'll cruise by the hideout later.
Well, guys, see you then!
‐Later days, teach!
‐"Goodbye" is more proper.
I can't picture Aya and Kazu liking each other.
Yeah, me neither, but the good thing is,
she's always got someone with her now.
Mm‐hmm.
Um, you guys, I... I just wanted to say thank you.
Why?
I think it's awesome how you're going
around making sure none of us are alone.
Both of my parents work,
and nothing felt worse than me getting
home and the house being empty.
It's pretty awesome how you kept Kayo and
Aya and me from being alone all the time.
So thank you.
Hey, guys! We going to the hideout or what?
I'm getting tired of waiting.
- ‐What's up? Where's Kazu?
- ‐ He went to go meet Aya.
‐How come?
‐You're joking, right?
It's not like she doesn't know where our hideout is.
Maybe you should talk to him.
Oh, whatever.
Let's get going, already!
OK.
Goodbye, Mr. Yashiro.
‐ Slow pokes
‐ What's the rush?
Wait up, guys!
Aya Nakanishi,
Hiromi Sugita,
and Kayo Hinazuki.
They're all still alive,
so I guess that means the killer gave up on them.
But now that the clues from the bus are gone,
how am I gonna find him?
There. Now he really looks like a girl.
Whoa!
Now what? Are you done?
You know, playing detective.
Not yet.
I'm still on the case.
In 2006, my mom told Sawada she
thought she knew who the killer was.
It's possible it's someone she knows now, in 1988.
Maybe like Mr. Yashiro and his candy,
the killer needs, a substitute, too,
someone to take the place of the kids that got away.
Move it.
Well, me and Kenya are heading out
now to go watch the hockey game.
‐Is Hamada playing?
‐You know it.
Wish I could go. When you see
him, tell him I said good luck.
‐Sure.
‐See ya later.
Here I am.
You notice how Misato's been keeping to herself lately?
No. Really?
Yeah.
People have been avoiding her,
ever since that lunch money thing happened.
Oh, man. I guess I could try talking to her on Monday.
Cool.
Thanks for breakfast!
Oh, yeah,
I might be a little late today.
Not too late, I hope.
When you know what time,
how about you call and let me know, OK?
Mm‐hmm, I will.
See ya later, Mom!
Have a good day today, Satoru.
‐ Mr. Yashiro's gonna take us.
‐ Really?
You know who will have to walk over there.
‐ Too bad for her.
‐ What can I say to her?
Crap! Missed her.
Satoru, I heard you're gonna try helping Misato next.
Mm‐hmm, but she just left.
I bet she's going to Wakaba Gym.
‐Really?
‐Yeah, Hamada's playing,
so Mr. Yashiro invited her to go cheer him on.
You know what,
she went to last week's game alone, too.
‐Thanks.
‐Want us to go with you?
Nah, I think I better do this myself.
It's no biggie.
OK, but I want a full report tomorrow.
Got it, Detective Satoru?
Sure.
We'll be at the hideout if you need backup.
- ‐Mm‐hmm. See you later!
- ‐ Later, dude!
- ‐ See you tomorrow!
- ‐ You got it.
‐ Bye! ‐ See ya!
‐ Bye, you guys!
Saying bye's a big deal with him.
I know, right?
He acts like he'll never see us again.
Whoa! It's even colder in here than outside.
Ohhh! Hamada!
Show 'em who's boss out there.
I can't concentrate with you uglies yellin'!
‐Ah, we can yell if we want.
‐Watch the attitude, Kouichi.
‐Otherwise, no dinner for you.
‐What? But they're bugging me!
There she is.
And she's alone.
-All right, guys, warm up and get your game face on.
- Yes, sir!
Now the killer's lost two more potential victims,
it makes sense he'd go for her next.
She's a perfect target.
She's going to the bathroom.
Game starts in five!
You got it, coach!
Why is she taking so long?
I needed a candy break. What's wrong?
The game's about to start.
Are you standing guard for someone?
Huh? Oh, uh... no.
I just wanted to talk to Misato.
Misato. Hmm...
Huh.
‐What, did she go outside?
‐Uh‐huh.
Where did she take off to?
That's Yuuki's dad's truck.
Mr. Yashiro,
I need to follow someone.
- ‐Will you drive?
- ‐ Hmm.
That doesn't even sound legal.
It's nothing bad.
We're just playing detective.
We pretend there's a kidnapper at large.
Then we try to find girls who seem like they're lonely
and make friends with them.
If anything, we could end up stopping a real kidnapping.
My God, it might be just a game, but it's a good idea.
I'm glad you think so.
Satoru, better buckle up.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
I have to get that fixed.
There.
So, you've noticed Misato's
been keeping to herself lately.
Actually, Hiromi told me a little while ago.
Well, if you ask me,
it's great you're being so proactive about it.
I don't know about that.
I couldn't get up the nerve to talk to her before,
and, well, I started thinking
she might make good bait.
Really? Bait.
So you're out to catch someone.
Now I know why you were working so
hard to be friendly and outgoing.
You’re a man on a mission.
Mm‐hmm. Everybody has something that's
missing from their lives, even me.
If I can fill that void...
Crap.
I just fed him his own line.
You and I have a lot in common.
That happens to be my philosophy in life.
When I teach a sixth‐grade class,
I like to bring it up in my graduation speech.
It sort of ties into what you said,
about using Misato as bait?
I can tell you regret it,
but in my opinion, you shouldn't.
There's no difference between
a good deed and a bad one.
They both have a similar goal,
to satisfy a need within a person.
Well, that's... extreme.
For example, lately I've tried all kinds
of things to get closer to someone.
Sometimes I'm direct,
other times I play coy.
At times,
I've even been deceitful.
And boy, it's been fun.
With who? A girlfriend?
I can see how you'd make that connection.
Hmm. Either way,
it's about filling some kind of emptiness.
Um... want a lollipop?
Thank you for asking,
but I'm afraid you won't find any there.
You see, this isn't my car.
Where is your car then? In the shop?
Whatever your happiest moment is today,
another will eventually come along to replace it.
And thanks to you, mine just got replaced.
Nothing compares to the feeling a person gets
when they can finally satisfy their need.
You spent all this time searching,
and when you get it, it's like heaven.
You know, it's true what they say,
the more effort something takes,
the sweeter the reward is.
Where the hell is he going with this?
Laxatives?
Satoru. You lied to me a few minutes ago.
You said you're just pretending there's a kidnapper,
but the truth is, you know there's one,
and you're trying to catch him.
I've resisted the idea for a while now
because I couldn't believe it was possible.
Well, more like I didn't want to believe...
the possibility that someone
was anticipating my every move.
If you're still worried about Misato, don't be.
The only person in that truck is Jun Shiratori's father.
I realized something was up with you the
day I saw you following Aya Nakanishi.
And I was planning to kidnap her
the day I gave you and your mom a ride.
Looking back, it's kind of funny.
I mean, there you were trying to snatch my prey
and I was the one telling you how to do it.
That was the second time you ruined my plans,
and I started to suspect it was more than a coincidence.
I knew Misato's friends were shunning her,
so I asked her to the hockey game.
Then I told Hiromi about it.
If you showed up,
my suspicions were correct,
that you...
you were my enemy.
No way.
When the time was right,
I gave Misato a drink
laced with that laxative you found.
And I bought dinner,
to place Shiratori at the scene.
No. No!
Yes, sir, all the pieces fit together as planned.
And in the end,
I'm not who you thought I was.
Oh, and about the car,
I borrowed this one earlier.
I was looking for something specific for today.
Generic model, generic paint job.
A car that's so ubiquitous, no one would even miss it.
You know, this is the first time
I've put that theory into practice.
How could I be so stupid?!
It was so obvious.
Thanks to you, Kayo's alive.
I just couldn't accept the possibility.
Yashiro was on one of Sawada's lists of suspects.
But my mom's name was right there with his,
so I figured the list was bullshit and blew it off.
I trusted him so much, I couldn't even think
of him as a suspect, let alone the killer.
But...
he is.
And now he's got me right where he wants me.
It started snowing.
Don't.
It's stuck for good.
The game's over.
For you and me.
You know,
I still can't believe it.
You anticipated all my plans
and destroyed them one by one.
I'm stunned how easily you caught me,
a little boy like you.
It's almost like you can see the future or something.
I want to make sure you understand why you have to die.
Yes, you ruined my plans,
but this has nothing to do with revenge.
Believe me, I do respect you.
But if I can't satisfy my needs the usual way,
I have to find an alternative.
You don't have to do this.
You said the game was over!
The children of this town are safe thanks to you, Satoru.
So congratulations, you got what you wanted.
And as for what I wanted, I still get to
kill someone for my sake and on my terms.
Yashiro, I'm not gonna die until I
see you hang for what you've done!
Yes, well,
keep telling yourself that.
Yashiro!
You son of a bitch!
I'll get you for this!
I wish I could stay, but I have so much packing to do.
Yashiro!
I know your future!
Shit.
It's cold.
Come on, come on!
Going numb...
Shit...
Mom?
What's up, kiddo?
I looked up, our eyes met...
My friends...
Hi, Satoru!
Thank you, Satoru.
Kayo.
Airi.