I think my dad left because he couldn't bear
everyone in town thinking he was a thief.
And Mom, I bet her not believing him either
was really what bothered him the most.
The whole thing made me want
to stop trusting people.
I felt like I was being forced
to choose sides.
I thought, if I hated my mom or my
dad, maybe I'd feel better.
Then a few years later,
I heard my mom say,
"Why couldn't I just believe him?"
Then I knew she was miserable too.
And then,
when I heard her say that,
I decided to keep on trusting
and loving them both.
I realized that if there's
one thing I'm really good at,
it's believing in people.
Wha...
What the hell?
I just saw Airi
go inside.
Then she might be stuck
and can't get out. Hey!
Airi!
Airi, can you hear me?!
Airi! We gotta go.
She's heavy.
Hang on, I'll get you
out of here.
Crap!
I can't lug her down by myself.
‐What are you doing?
‐You manga guys really should hit the gym more often.
Let's hurry before we get barbecued.
Get going out the back.
I got her from here.
Don't get her mixed up in your shit.
Guess I get to be the hero today.
I hope Airi's OK.
How did that fire start?
Was it an accident or..
the killer?
Wait.
He was trying to kill Airi with that fire.
And he was trying to frame me for it.
That's why she gave me her phone,
so the cops wouldn't find the email.
He knew where she lived.
Maybe he followed her or...
maybe she knows him.
Whoever he is, he's close.
I'm gonna find him.
And with any luck,
I'll get to him before the cops catch me.
This stop Koiwa.
Make sure you have
your belongings before...
Hello? Hello?
All right, who is this?
Satoru Fujinuma.
If you're who you say you are,
then nice to meet ya.
I've been expecting your call.
Sure, I'd be glad to.
But not here.
Someplace public.
No, I'm not telling you
who I am just yet.
Tomorrow, when we meet.
'Cause if you're not who you say you are,
then you're the son of a bitch that killed Sachiko.
‐
‐ Sit down anywhere.
Oh, hey, Satoru. Over here.
I'm Sawada.
I used to work with your mom at Ishikari TV.
Goddamn, you look just like Sachiko.
Yeah, you're her kid,
no doubt about it.
It's him.
I bet you're wondering if you can trust me.
But there's nothing to worry about.
I didn't tell the cops you called
and I didn't kill your mom.
Yeah, well, maybe you think
I killed her.
‐ Not even.
‐How can you be sure?
'Cause I knew your mom
and I know she didn't raise
the kind of son who'd kill her.
Hmm, I see.
Yeah, I remembered
I had it in my pocket yesterday.
You're in it deep,
that's for sure.
Tell me about it.
And now I'm on the run
'cause I panicked.
I can't stop screwing things up.
What happened happened,
so it's pointless to beat yourself up about it.
That's something your mom liked to say.
It's kind of appropriate, don't you think?
You want me to tell you what we
talked about the other day?
Yeah.
Do you remember 18 years ago,
when that serial killer was targeting kids?
Yeah, sure.
Jun Shiratori's still sitting on death row
and still denying he killed them.
Well, Satoru was right about him.
Shiratori's innocent,
and I think I've figured out who the real killer is.
Can you meet me at Koiwa station tomorrow?
I should have asked for the guy's name.
Anyway, let's talk about
what happened back then.
- ‐About how Kayo Hinazuki died.
- ‐
We know that on the night of March the 2nd,
Kayo's mom and her boyfriend beat
her and locked her in the shed.
That was around 10:00, and she was still alive.
We know she froze to death,
and we also know that when the mom and the
boyfriend found her body the next morning,they hid it.
'cause they didn't want to take the fall for the murder.
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
The theory goes that Kayo was taken
from the shed sometime after 10 p. m.
At about 12:30, Kayo's mom went
out to get her and found her gone.
Then she called your house and asked
your mom if she knew where Kayo was.
When they arrested
Jun Shiratori,
the only evidence they had that tied him to
the crime was a pair of rubber boots he owned.
The tread matched tracks
they found near the shed.
Here's how the police figured the killing went down.
First he knocked her out and took some pictures of her.
Next, he put her in the walk‐in freezer
at work and sprayed her with water.
As soon as her temperature dropped to
20Â°, she was brain‐dead.
He waited around for about 30
minutes to make sure she was gone.
Then, just before dawn,
he put her body back in the shed.
There's no way Yuuki killed her.
Kayo Hinazuki,
Hiromi Sugita and Aya Nakanishi...
Just before those three went missing,
the same exact thing happened in
the next town over from yours.
Someone was quickly arrested,
but he swore he was innocent, same as Shiratori.
You see?
Same crime, same pattern.
It's beyond coincidental.
- ‐That means...
- ‐ Exactly.
I've been trying to tell people for years.
They called me crazy,
but in the end, I was right.
These crimes were never really solved.
The killer framed every suspect.
So whoever murdered Kayo also murdered Sachiko!
He's still on the loose.
In this city.
This bastard's beyond clever.
He plants a false trail of
evidence at the scene of the crime
that leads the cops away from him
and straight toward some other poor sucker.
And while everyone looks the other way,
he kills again.
This is too much.
You think he'll try it again?
If Fujinuma shows his face here,
I'm gonna take his ass out personally.
So what's the story
with the high school girl?
She was in it with him.
Yeah, but he didn't
want any loose threads,
so he tried to kill her too to shut her up.
Dragging her into this shit.
What an asshole.
They're wrong.
Please, Airi, you don't have
to apologize for anything.
Your uncle's right.
We didn't know there was a stalker after you.
You must have been so terrified.
‐But, Auntie,that's not..
‐You poor thing.
We shouldn't have left you all
alone in the house like that.
‐ You're wrong.
‐The police know who it is and they'll catch him soon.
You have nothing to worry about now.
They're all wrong.
Everyone thinks Satoru killed
his mom and tried to kill me.
But that's crazy.
It doesn't matter what I say,
no one believes me.
You sure the message was sent from Sachiko's phone?
Yeah.
Before I could get Airi out of the house,
she slipped her phone in my pocket.
Check it out.
You weren't kidding.
Looks like he wanted to help the cops catch you
by pinning the fire on you too.
But why go to all that trouble?
I'm already a suspect in one murder.
Uh‐uh.
This wasn't about framing me.
He was after Airi for another reason.
Do you think he tried to kill her
because she had something on him?
To get me to take the fall for my mom's murder,
he had to know when I'd be home to find her.
That means he new my schedule.
So in the 24 hours between when my mom
saw him try to kidnap that little girl
and when he killed my mom,
he must have gone to the pizza place
and had a look at the shift schedule.
If that's what happened,
I bet Airi saw his face.
He might even be someone I've seen before.
It's possible.
All we have to do is find out who got behind the
counter that day and we might have our killer.
Hell, it's worth a shot.
It might even break this case wide open.
‐I'm off to the hospital.
‐Uh... OK.
There's a report on the murders
from 18 years ago on my computer.
You should check it out.
I have a theory that Jun Shiratori might
suspect his father to be the killer.
Shiratori's refusal to talk to
authorities did not help his case.
Perhaps he did not want to say anything
that could possibly incriminate his father.
That figures.
Yuuki loved his dad.
Kayo Hinazuki's classmates testified they had
seen her and Shiratori together many times.
The investigators focused on their testimonies,
while ignoring Satoru Fujinuma's.
Suspects.
I don't know any of them besides Yuuki and his dad.
They only had five?
The investigators thought
Hiromi Sugita was murdered
because the killer
mistook him for a girl.
Based on this assumption,
they made a list of five suspects,
none of whom knew Hiromi Sugita.
PE today is folk dancing.
Eww! That sucks ass.
I don't wanna hold some ugly girl's hand.
But I'd be OK holding Hiromi's.
Oh... that's gutsy.
I think I know why Hiromi was murdered.
The killer knew he was a boy.
He only killed him to cover his tracks,
to keep his name off the list.
Jun Shiratori was arrested after someone in the neighborhood
reported seeing him talking to a third‐grade girl.
The girl was alone at the time.
In the storage room of Shiratori Foods,
police found photos of Hiromi Sugita's body.
From these photos, investigators suspected Jun
Shiratori of having pedophiliac tendencies,
and magazines popular with
pedophiles were found in his room,
confirming their suspicions.
He didn't have that shit.
The killer planted that stuff
to keep the cops off his trail.
Who were the suspects before Hiromi died?
Ten to one,
the killer's name's on it.
- ‐ ‐ Ms.
-  Katagiri, are you awake?
Excuse me,
I'm visiting someone, but...
- ‐Is the bathroom that way?
- ‐ Yes.
Her name wouldn't be listed.
201 is vacant.
That's it.
‐She's sound asleep.
‐Thanks for the update.
Oh, one side!
I gotta pee like a mother.
Ms. Katagiri.
Sorry to barge in on you like this.
You wouldn't happen
to be be Satoru Fujinuma, hmm?
Huh? Uh, no.
Actually, I'm a friend of Satoru's.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Airi's mother.
Satoru didn't do what the police are saying.
I know he didn't kill his mom,
and he wasn't trying to kill me either.
He didn't set that fire.
He was the one who saved me from it.
You're confused,
after breathing all that smoke.
Your manager got you out
of the house in time.
I don't know what they've told you,
but none of it's true.
They're even saying I helped him kill his mom.
The worst part about all this is... no one believes me.
No one believes Satoru either, and he's all alone now.
Airi,
even after all these years,
I still think about your father.
I should have gone after him.
I believe you, hon.
Hurry up now.
Go and find Satoru.
Oh, crap.
I forgot to turn it off.
You left it on!
Thank God.
Airi, are you OK?
Oh, yeah,
I'm good as new.
But I need to see you.
Can you meet me under the you‐know‐what?
Wait, no, don't go there.
-I got you in enough trouble..
-Don't worry, I'll make sure no one follows me, promise.
- ‐ And go!
- ‐ Yeah, let's follow it!
Meeting her isn't a good idea.
I could have asked if she saw
someone peeking at the schedule.
The more she gets involved,
the worse it's gonna be for her.
That sucked.
‐It doesn't fly that far at all.
‐Yeah, how come?
The wings are straight.
If you do this,
it'll give it more aerodynamic lift.
Are you sure that's really gonna help it?
Try it out.
No way, it worked!
Look, it's heading for the river!
What's a grown‐up doing
here at this time of day?
Is he out of work?
I hope he's not a pervert.
Poor Yuuki.
I bet he had to hear the same thing back then.
- ‐ See? I made it.
- ‐ Yeah.
And I made sure no one followed,
like I promised.
Cool.
I feel terrible.
For a sec there,
I thought this might be a trap by the cops.
I said that out loud.
You better be thinking like that.
You're a fugitive so you can't take any chances.
Anyway,
I'm glad you trusted me enough to meet me.
Yeah.
At work...
I'd say Mr. Nishizono is pretty sketchy.
‐Nishizono?
‐I've seen him once or twice.
He's on the city council 'cause he wears that pen.
The boss is always kissing his butt, too.
When they meet,
it's always been in the boss's office,
so he could totally peek at the
schedule and get my address.
Hah, I even said hi to him.
The list didn't have a Nishizono on it.
Maybe it's a fake name.
No, he couldn't use a fake name
if he's on the city council.
I think he came after me 'cause I saw his face before.
That's not coming together.
Goddamn it.
There's still a piece missing.
Satoru,
I know how you must be feeling,
but you can't beat yourself up.
I try and try.
I can never make things right.
‐Hmm?
‐Oh, nothing.
It's an idea for a manga I had.
The Grim Reaper makes a scheduling error
and the kid dies on the wrong day.
He tries to bring the kid back to life,
but it backfires.
Someone else dies,
so he tries again,
and someone else suffers.
He just wants to do the right thing,but ...
everyone he meets ends up one way or the other,
miserable or dead.
So are you saying you're kind of like that Grim Reaper?
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm saying.
You're an idiot.
Do I look dead?
And as for being miserable or whatever,
what does he know? That's his opinion.
Your Grim Reaper character should
have a little more faith in himself.
I think it's too soon to give up on what
you want 'cause nothing's set in stone.
However this ends is still up in the air,
and no one knows what it's gonna be yet.
Airi,
I'm really glad I got to meet you.
I said that out loud.
Satoru Fujinuma.
‐Run, Satoru!
‐Out of the way!
Airi!
Satoru Fujinuma,
you're under arrest
for murder, attempted murder, and arson.
4:50 p. m.,
suspect apprehended.
He didn't do it! Let me go! He's innocent!
He didn't kill anyone! Satoru!
I knew me and Airi wouldn't last.
Either I'd get caught or Revival would make it disappear.
Here it is,
the last time I'll ever see her.
I know what I should do.
Satoru! I'm sorry!
I didn't tell 'em you were here!
I swear I didn't tell 'em!
They followed me! I'm sorry, Satoru!
I have to leave her with some kind of hope.
Just like she did for me.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
This is all my fault!
What would a superhero say at a time like this?
Isn't it hard having to fight bad guys by yourself?
It's not your fault.
I know I'll get through this somehow,
'cause I know you believe in me.
So thank you, Airi.
I'm glad I trusted you.