[C.C.] Lelouch, a young,
outcast prince of Britannia,
possesses two great powers:
One of them is Geass,
the absolute ability to compel
any person to do
whatever he commands.
[The other is the Black
Knights, his military force
assembled with the intent of
destroying
the Britannian Empire
ruled by his father.
Veiling his true identity behind
a mask and the code name Zero,
Lelouch has made his move
to avenge his mother's murder
and to create a world in which
his younger sister Nunnally
can find happiness.
What will be the final
outcome of these actions?
At this point,
no one can predict.
[LELOUCH]
Hm? A Britannian?
Looks too confident to be a spy.
An extremist?
[C.C.] Isn't it wonderful
how the number of recruits
keeps growing?
And it was simpler
than I ever expected.
"While I bitterly hate
the Britannians,
I refuse to condone terrorism."
That's the prevailing view
of most Elevens.
[C.C.] Then basically, Elevens
support the Black Knights
for the most part.
[LELOUCH]
Which in turn,
makes it easier for us
to operate as a whole.
It's a huge help that the people
don't report our activities
to the Britannians.
Plus, I hear some
group called "Kyoto"
offered to send us
some Knightmares.
The number of informants has
been increasing quickly, too.
The Japanese can't resist
jumping on the bandwagon.
They hear a well-grounded
buzzword, and off they go.
[C.C.] Hence the big
"Knights for Justice" act?
Yeah, well,
everybody loves a hero.
And what better
hero than a knight.
[C.C. giggles]
I kinda doubt that's what a real
Knight for Justice would say.
[LELOUCH]
You don't think so?
Yes, I was demoted
from my position.
In very much the same
way that you were.
[JEREMIAH growls]
[VILETTA] We have no intention
of letting the situation
end this way. And we have
the sneaking suspicion
that you don't, either.
[DIETHARD]
That so? Well, who can say?
We have a lead that
might help us find Zero!
[DIETHARD gasps]
[VILETTA] You're familiar
with Ashford Private Academy?
I want to investigate a male
student attending there.
I think he may be
working with Zero.
[JEREMIAH] Viletta and I
are going to be shipping out
with the military soon for duty,
and we'll be stationed in
the Narita mountains.
Therefore...
[DIETHARD]
Narita?
Isn't that where the Japan
Liberation Front headquarters
are rumored to be located?
You may be a bit too clever
for your own good.
Heh, you overestimate me.
Wow, it's amazing!
[BLACK KNIGHT B]
These are Glasgows, aren't they?
[BLACK KNIGHT C]
Burais. A Japanese modification.
[BLACK KNIGHT D]
I've never seen these before!
[BLACK KNIGHT E]
Man, the Black Knights
have got some serious muscle!
[BLACK KNIGHT F] It wasn't
easy to sign up with the B.K.
[BLACK KNIGHT G]
So, that makes us special, huh?
We're elite!
[BLACK KNIGHT H]
I'm totally amped!
Those guys from Kyoto,
they believe in us.
They sent us this.
[YOSHIDA] A completely-made
Japanese Knightmare!
[KALLEN]
The Guren MK-II.
[MINAMI]
Did you check out the manual?
[INOUE] The Radiant Wave
Surger? What a weapon!
Heh, heh!
I'm really lovin' this!
The big shots in Kyoto
are recognizing us!
We've got their approval!
[BLACK KNIGHT D]
Tamaki-san!
[TAMAKI]
Huh?
[BLACK KNIGHT D] Would you show
me how to use this equipment?
[TAMAKI]
Oh, sure, hang on!
I'll be right there!
[INOUE]
Newbies. What're you gonna do?
[ZERO] First Tamaki,
and now Inoue and the rest
are treating this like a party.
Ah...
[ZERO]
Kyoto is backing multiple
resistance groups, correct?
Yes, which means that
we finally made it in.
They know that we're worthy.
[ZERO]
No, you're wrong there, Kallen.
This is merely a test
they've put to us.
[KALLEN] So, what if it is?
This is still incredible!
[ZERO]
You are an optimist.
What's this?
[ZERO] The Guren MK-II
is yours now, Kallen.
Mine?! But we have
a lot more people now,
and we can't afford
to lose you.
We need the Guren's
defenses to protect you--
[ZERO]
You're a top-notch pilot.
I'm a commander.
I'll use a Burai,
but you're our only ace
to play during a battle.
Besides, you have
reason to fight.
[gasps]
Right.
[OHGI]
Zero. You got a second?
We got some weird intel
here from a Britannian
who wants to join up
with the Black Knights.
[ZERO]
Hmm?
[OHGI] This may be
a trap to draw us out.
I'd say even if we want
to confirm the information,
it's too risky to
contact him directly.
But news like this isn't
something we can just ignore.
What should we do?
[ZERO] This weekend,
we're going hiking.
What?
[ZERO]
To the Narita mountains.
Very well, then.
[NUNNALLY] Sayoko,
we won't need any breakfast
for my brother this morning.
[SAYOKO]
He's going out?
He'll be leaving on a
three-day trip starting today.
Oh, I see.
My, your brother's been
going out quite a bit recently.
Think it's a girlfriend?
[NUNNALLY sighs]
Maybe it is...
[GUARD A]
Sector 5, nothing to report.
Right.
The next scheduled report
will be in two hours.
[GUARD B] Of course
there's nothing to report.
This area's controlled by
the Japan Liberation Front.
No one can just stroll in-- Huh?
[GUARD A]
Huh?
Zero!
[ZERO]
Relax. I only came to talk.
I want you to ignore any unusual
activity during your watch.
[GUARD A]
Sure, no problem.
[GUARD B]
C'mon, it's your turn.
[GUARD A]
What's the rush?
We're just on
regular duty, y'know?
[OHGI] I've confirmed
the signal from Zero.
We're now moving to way point 2.
[TAMAKI] Hey, why doesn't Zero
just use the radio in his Burai?
[INOUE] What d'ya suppose he
meant when he said "hiking"?
[YOSHIDA]
Uh, military training, right?
[TAMAKI] Only with
Zero in another location?
[MINAMI]
Maybe we'll dig a hot spring.
[SUGIYAMA] Is that why we
brought those excavators?
Then hell, I'm all for it.
[TAMAKI] Kallen,
you heard anything about this?
[gulps]
I haven't.
[TAMAKI]
You, Ohgi?
Nope, not a word.
[OHGI] Zero isn't using the
radio to avoid being traced.
Is he serious about this?
The day I've waited for
has finally come, Cornelia.
Hmm?
[LELOUCH gasps]
[DARLTON] We're certain that
the Japan Liberation Front's
headquarters are in this area.
We've already split four
battalions into seven units
and hidden them in the vicinity.
We've only to wait for
the viceroy's signal,
then we'll surround them in one
fell swoop and wipe them out.
And are you confident
that the enemy won't show up
outside the encirclement line?
[DARLTON]
Hmm?
[CORNELIA]
You mean Zero?
Have no fear about that.
As the operation begins,
we'll be blocking off
the surrounding highways
and mountain roads, also.
[CORNELIA]
Plus, we have reserve units.
If Zero's stupid enough to show
up, it'll be the end of him.
[MILLY]
What?!
You wanna meet her?!
Are you kidding?!
Do you know who
you're talking about?!
She's a princess and
you're just a citizen.
What do you have in common
aside from that hoteljacking?
Yes, but...
As for Princess Euphemia...
I never got to thank her.
[MILLY] Hmm... There was a time
when my family name
had the influence
to arrange that.
So tell me, Nina, do you
know what the social status is
of a Principal's granddaughter?
Um... not a very high one?
Correct. Not very.
[LELOUCH]
C.C.! What are you doing here?
I said that I would
protect you, didn't I?
[LELOUCH]
Aren't you over doing it?
I've been wondering
about something, Lelouch.
Why are you Lelouch?
[LELOUCH] I don't have time
to discuss philosophy with you.
You changed your family
surname to Lamperouge,
but you kept Lelouch, the name
that was given to you at birth.
How sentimental.
You can't let go of the past.
[LELOUCH] Well, C.C. swings to
the other extreme, doesn't it?
It's not a human name.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[C.C.] Lelouch... do you know
why snow is white?
[LELOUCH]
Hmm...?
Snow is white
because it's forgotten
what color it's supposed to be.
[STAFF OFFICER]
All units are in position.
[CORNELIA]
Understood.
Euphemia will provide logistical
support from G1, as planned.
Have her command
the medical group.
[STAFF OFFICER]
Yes, Your Highness.
[GUILFORD]
Princess Cornelia...
Guilford, let me guess:
This is about Euphy, isn't it?
[GUILFORD]
Yes.
She really should be in
a government agency, not--
But she's being unusually
stubborn about this.
She told me she wanted to see
actual combat for herself.
[EUPHEMIA]
Hmm?
What's that unit there,
holding to the rear?
[SOLDIER A] Our reserve force
with an Eleven pilot.
What?! You mean
that's the Lancelot?
As a rule, Numbers
aren't permitted
to operate Knightmares, but that
particular unit is an exception.
[SOLDIER A] The second prince
is the patron of that unit.
We have no say over
their personnel selection.
But he said he wants them to
have as many chances
at real combat as possible.
[OHGI] Are you really
going through with this?
[ZERO] Our opponent is Cornelia,
whose forces are among
the best Britannia has to offer.
Then why don't we cooperate
with the Japan Liberation front?
[ZERO]
What was that?
Oghi, don't you
believe in me any more?
What d'you mean?!
I was the one who asked
you to be our leader!
Don't you remember?!
[ZERO] Then there's only
one answer to give.
[OHGI]
Uh. Right...
[DARLTON]
Viceroy, it's time.
[CORNELIA]
Right. Commence operation!
You, the Japan Liberation Front.
You, who time has left behind.
You, who have forgotten
basic human decency.
You and your dream of
a bygone golden age
shall fall and rot
to nothingness.
We're under enemy attack?!
Yes, sir! The Britannian
forces have completely
encircled the Narita mountains!
We've counted over 100 units!
[ZERO]
It's begun.
[growls]
Huh?! What the hell--?!
You've gotta be kidding, Zero!
Those troops coming in have this
whole area totally surrounded!
There's no way out!
[ZERO]
We've already been cut off!
Our only chance of
surviving now is to fight!
What?! We can't fight
the Britannians!
Lemme get this straight:
We're surrounded, and you
want us to fight them head on?!
And we'd be fighting
against Cornelia!
Her forces are far stronger
than any we've encountered!
[ZERO] Correct. It would be
a miracle if we win this.
[OHGI]
Zero, what're you saying?!
[ZERO] Even messiahs
need to perform miracles
if they're to be acknowledged!
Therefore, we have to produce
our own miracle, don't we?
Now look, pulling this off
isn't gonna be cheap!
The price could be our lives!
I knew it was insane
to make you our leader!
It should be me!
[OHGI gasps]
[TAMAKI whimpers]
[ZERO] Our path of
retreat has been cut off.
If you think you can win
without me, then shoot me.
Someone. Anyone.
[gasps]
[ZERO] Since you've
joined the Black Knights,
you have only two choices:
You may either live with me...
or you may perish with me!
[SOLDIER 1]
We're completely surrounded,
and our underground reserve
forces were captured
all at once!
[SOLDIER 2] General Katase,
we've received a message
from Cornelia's forces
demanding our surrender!
Imbecile! If we fall here,
then we've lost,
and the whole resistance
movement falls with us!
[JLF STAFF OFFICER 1]
Then, General...
[JLF STAFF OFFICER 2] Do we
engage the enemy in battle,
or do we dig in?
[KATASE]
What about Tohdoh? Where is he?!
[JLF STAFF OFFICER 3]
He's gone to Kyoto
to get the custom Burais!
[JLF STAFF OFFICER 1]
The four Holy Swords
are traveling with him, too.
[JLF STAFF OFFICER 2]
If they're on schedule,
they should be
returning soon, but...
[KATASE]
Tohdoh won't make it in time.
Prepare to send out the Burais!
We'll break the encirclement
on one side and evacuate!
We'll show them the
Japanese spirit and pride!
This is our moment of truth!
We believe that the
enemy's main base is located
in the mountains here, but
we haven't pinpointed it yet.
However, until we obtain a list
of their collaborators,
we can't burn down everything
with our aerial bombing.
[SOLDIER B] The enemy is
engaging our encirclement,
and they'll try to break
through at some point.
From there, we'll be able to
ascertain where their base is.
[SOLDIER A] Our forces are
divided into three fronts:
The units led by General Darlton
here, General Alex here,
and Viceroy Cornelia here.
As for our flanking
forces-- What...?
[gasps]
[SOLDIER B]
It's enemy ECM.
[DARLTON] The main enemy force
should be coming out
any time now. We're
switching to ECCM mode.
Link up on channel alpha-four!
The enemy--what are
we calling them again?
[SUBORDINATE]
Burais, sir.
Right. They're rather
like pseudo-Glasgows,
so watch out for em.
[SUBORDINATE]
Yes, my lord!
How clever. They turned this
whole mountain into a fortress.
[GUILFORD]
Your Highness, please fall back!
[CORNELIA] Guilford,
don't treat me as though
I'm another one of your women.
Princess Cornelia!
[JLF SOLDIER]
It's... Cornelia!
[JLF COMMANDER] Don't panic!
Take out the leader!
[CORNELIA]
Insolent worms!
[JLF COMMANDER screams]
[GUILFORD] Right. Well then,
I'll cover you from the rear.
[CORNELIA]
Heh.
Well?! Cornelia is here!
is there no one who
will challenge me?!
[ZERO]
What's wrong?
Challenge me,
and try to take me down!
All right, fine!
Do what you want!
We acknowledge you
as our leader, Zero.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
[ANNOUNCER] An evacuation order
has been issued for this area!
Anyone remaining
must evacuate at once!
I repeat, an evacuation
order has been...
[RESCH A]
Why did they choose this place?
If the military should find
the experimental data
on Code R, it's all over!
Oh my. Being inside
the terrorist's area,
we thought it would be difficult
for them to discover us.
This was all General
Bartley's decision,
so there's no use
complaining about it.
They're too fragile.
[DARLTON] The enemy seems
to be concentrated over here.
This may be the target!
Split up now!
[SOLDIER 6] No good! Our second
attack wave had no effect!
Their sheer dominance
is insurmountable!
[SUBORDINATE] General Darlton,
based on the analysis
of the enemy's movements,
I've determined that the
entrance to the JLF
main base is that lodge
located up on that mountain.
I believe the proper word
for this situation is "bingo."
[SUBORDINATE] Well, to be
more precise, sir, it'd be--
Oh, just call it in
already, Mr. Literal.
[CORNELIA]
Is that... Darlton?
So, that's where the
main enemy base is located?
[CORNELIA] Right. We'll be
securing our position here.
Are you sure about this?
[CORNELIA] I don't need
to steal achievements
from my subordinates.
Send the reserve force
to back up Darlton!
Looks like he'll be
getting another medal.
[LELOUCH]
Impressive as always, Cornelia.
A very logical deployment.
However, excellent though
it is, it's also easy to read.
As is your location.
I thought the reserve units
were supposed to be assigned
to General Darlton?
[VILETTA]
That's right, they were.
But our unit has to secure the
rear line of Viceroy Cornelia.
[JEREMIAH]
You mean this is the rear line?!
You can't get any farther
away from the battlefield!
How am I going to redeem
my reputation out here
if I'm not even
near the fighting?!
[JLF SOLDIER 2] We've lost
contact with Nakamura's unit!
[JLF SOLDIER 3]
No response from Sector 3!
[JLF SOLDIER 4]
Major Tabata's been killed!
[JLF SOLDIER 2]
Kuroda and Kurata are gone, too!
[JLF SOLDIER 4]
What about Nagai?!
Where is Tohdoh?!
If only he were here,
the divine wind would blow!
We'd have another
miracle of Itsukushima!
[GUARD A]
Look out!
[ASAHINA] Sir, don't you think
this is a little extreme?
Asahina, Chiba!
Prep the custom Burais ASAP!
Tell Urabe and Senba
behind us to do the same.
Traffic is blocked off
all around Narita,
and they've already
begun to attack!
I just pray that we're in time.
Now, any resistance
still remaining in Area 11...
...will soon be finished.
Right! All preparations
have now been completed!
Black Knights,
prepare to move out!
[BLACK KNIGHT A]
Dammit, we have no choice!
[BLACK KNIGHT B]
I don't wanna die!
[BLACK KNIGHT C]
We'll make a miracle happen!
[BLACK KNIGHT E]
Yeah, we'll have Zero with us!
[LELOUCH] We, the Black Knights,
are going to launch
a surprise attack
on the Britannians
from the summit of the mountain!
Per my instructions,
you will charge en masse
down toward point three!
And the intent of this operation
is to capture Cornelia,
second princess of Britannia!
Our breakthrough route will be
opened by the Guren MK-II.
[LELOUCH] Kallen! Use
penetrating electrode number 3!
Settle things with one blow!
Got it!
[KALLEN]
Output confirmed.
Wave surger levels
ready and holding.
[sighs]
Activating gauntlet now!
It worked!
--[screaming]
--[KATASE] What's happening?!
[SOLDIER 6]
I-Is this an earthquake?!
[SOLDIER 7]
At a time like this?! [screams]
[DARLTON]
What the hell?!
[EUPHEMIA]
What's happening?!
Impossible! How could a
landslide come out of nowhere?!
[SOLDIER A] Alex's and Darlton's
units are getting wiped out!
[DARLTON]
Climb! Get to higher ground!
[CORNELIA]
Status report!
[SUBORDINATE]
We're still trying to confirm!
[GUILFORD]
Your Highness, pull back!
You're in danger there!
I don't care!
Forget about me!
Find out about Darlton!
And where is Alex?!
[KATASE]
Will this place hold together?!
[JLF STAFF OFFICER 1]
The central area
should make it through!
[LLOYD]
Oh, my!
At this rate, they'll be swept
all the way to the bottom.
These heat readings
are abnormal.
Do you believe a
hydro-volcanic eruption
was artificially induced?
[LLOYD]
Impossible. Unless, of course,
someone's used Rakshata's
Radiant Wave Surger.
[SUZAKU]
Has something happened?
[LLOYD]
Uh-huh...
But it has nothing
to do with us,
so just relax and
continue waiting.
Ah...
[LELOUCH]
Hmph...
It's even more destructive
than I anticipated.
We did succeed in
isolating Cornelia's unit,
but we could have been
a bit more accurate.
Perhaps I should have
consulted a physics teacher?
Or asked Nina to
tutor me in probability?
[STAFF OFFICER]
New enemy force confirmed
moving in from the summit.
Carius unit is moving
to engage them.
Hoping to take advantage of
all the confusion, are they?
[STAFF OFFICER] Emergency call
from Carius unit!
What's wrong?
[STAFF OFFICER] It's not
the Japan Liberation Front!
They think it's...
the Black Knights!
[CORNELIA]
What?! Then it's...
Zero!
How dare he show up here?!
ZERO!
Lord Jeremiah, you can't
just abandon your post!
[JEREMIAH]
This requires drastic measures!
If you want glory in life,
then follow me!
[LELOUCH] Cornelia has only
limited reinforcements
headed her way.
Smash right through them!
[MINAMI]
Yeah! We can do this now!
All right, everybody,
you know the game plan.
Our job is to watch their backs!
Get ready... FIRE!
The enemy's taken out
Carius' unit?!
If I can finish this before Zero
reaches Princess Cornelia,
then I'll be golden!
[VILETTA]
Lord Jeremiah!
Viletta, you came!
I knew that you would!
[LELOUCH]
Burn the bridges behind you,
and keep your back to the wall.
Classical strategies remain
effective ones, don't they?
[JEREMIAH]
Zero!
[MINAMI]
Ugh! Dammit!
[JEREMIAH] Is Zero here?!
If he is, then face me!
Come forward, and fight
Jeremiah Gottwald!
[LELOUCH] Well, well...
it's been a while, Jeremiah.
So, you're still in the army?
I'd love to stay and
catch up,
but I'm afraid I don't have time
right this minute, "Orange boy."
O-Ora-a-a-a-a-a-a... Orange?!
DIE!
[JEREMIAH gasps]
Lord Jeremiah!
[JEREMIAH] Stay out of this!
This is my duel!
[VILETTA]
But look at it!
I've never seen a Knightmare
like that before!
Is it possible that
the Elevens have--
[JEREMIAH] You think Elevens are
capable of such technology?!
It's fast!
[JEREMIAH]
This thing...
Is this what destroyed
Carius' unit?!
Yeah, that's right, Britannia!
We can finally go up against you
on an equal footing, head on!
And our counterattack begins
with this baby, the Guren MK-II!
[yells]
[JEREMIAH]
Oh, hell!
There's something
on its right hand!
But if I keep my distance...
What's this?!
Sorry.
[JEREMIAH gasps]
Wha-What the hell's happening?!
[VILETTA]
Lord Jeremiah, eject!
I can't run now!
Zero's right in front of me!
He's standing right here!
Dammit! The auto-eject!
Don't you dare activate!
I can still get Zero...!
I know it!
I know I can still get him...!
[JEREMIAH rasps]
I won't lose. Not with this.
Guren MK-II!
She defeated Lord Jeremiah.
Who are the Black Knights?
Who are they, these warriors?!
All our tasks at hand
have been cleared.
The pieces are in position.
The only thing left to do is
check my opponent's stronghold.
[LELOUCH]
Decision time!
Even Cornelia will lose
with only limited
allied reinforcements.
Plus, we have the Guren MK-II.
I'll capture her.
Then at last I'll learn the
truth about my mother's death!
And once she's my prisoner...
I win.
Barring any unforeseen events,
my Black Knights
will claim victory!