[C.C.]
Situations evolve.
Our desires have
no bearing on that.
Time flows on,
unaffected by our struggles.
On this point,
Lelouch should be pleased,
for he possesses true
self-determination.
He can change destiny itself
by applying the absolute power
to compel anyone to obey him...
The power of Geass.
[TEACHER] Yes, it is true
that the invasion
by the Chinese Federation
and the terrorism
of the Black Knights
have disrupted our society.
But that is a completely
separate issue!
The fact remains you've both
been absent from class
far too often!
I don't care how
good your grades are
or that you're
Princess Euphemia's knight!
If you don't improve,
you will repeat this year!
Sounds like she's
still going strong.
She may carry on all night.
[LELOUCH sighs]
[YOUNG MAN] I'm telling you,
Zero's our savior!
Even Elevens can
move up in the world!
Just look at Suzaku Kururugi!
If it hadn't been for Zero,
the Chinese Federation
would have conquered Kyushu!
That isn't what
it said on the news.
Cause the Britannians
control the media.
I don't care,
as long as there's peace.
The peace of slavery?
That's what Kururugi wants!
[OHGI] So opinions
in the ghettos are split?
[MINAMI] Some are submissive,
some are defiant.
[SUGIYAMA]
But they'll all be shocked
when they find out
Zero's goal
is to start an
independent nation.
[YOSHIDA] Yeah, right,
that's totally crazy.
[MINAMI]
We need to be realistic.
[TAMAKI]
I agree with Zero.
[ALL]
Huh?
Well, isn't it true?
If we stick with him, we might
catch a huge lucky break.
Maybe I'll even get my dream
of being a bureaucrat.
A bureaucrat? Seriously?
Hey, even I had a dream once!
If I hadn't thrown in
with the Black Knights,
I'd probably be hooked
on Refrain by now!
[OHGI] Refrain might
bring back her memory
so I could find out
who Zero is.
But what would I do if I knew?
[KALLEN]
Ohgi?
On that other issue,
we wanted to ask
for instructions,
but we haven't
been able to reach Zero.
[OHGI] Then I'll just
go ahead as planned.
[TAMAKI] I'm telling you, don't.
It's a trap.
[KALLEN]
But we need inside sources.
They also said
there's someone there
who wants to join us.
Anyway, tomorrow
is the only time
we'll be able to use
the escape route
that Diethard set up for us.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for waiting!
The Ashford Academy
school festival,
which is the most open event
in the Tokyo settlement,
is about to start!
It will begin at
the sound of this voice!
Are you sure it's
all right to do this, Milly?
Very sure!
Okay.
[inhales]
[NUNNALLY]
Meow!
[CROWD cheering]
The school is
really noisy today.
Welcome! Step right up!
[GIRL]
Get your Britannian rolls!
[BOY] See the shocking
exposé: "The Zero Report!"
[GIRL] Photos!
Photos of Prince Clovis!
[LELOUCH]
That's what I thought.
So even Sawasaki and the others
turned out to be useful.
We've covered all
the tasks at hand.
[DIETHARD]
Yes.
We gathered all the sector data
on the emergency countermeasures
that they've left behind.
[LELOUCH]
The press?!
[DIETHARD] We've identified
the solar panels
used in each settlement as well
as the energy storage sites.
Oh, and what about
that collaborator issue?
[LELOUCH] I've handled
most of it myself.
About 72 percent is complete.
And Tohdoh?
[DIETHARD] He's drawing up
a list of occupation targets:
broadcasting stations and such.
I need you to check them
including the dummy plans
we're sending to Kyoto.
[LELOUCH] I understand.
I'll confirm tomorrow.
Oh, and I know we're late
in reporting this to you,
but regarding the operation
of the Zero Squad, Ohgi has...
[MILLY] There's trouble!
There's huge, huge trouble!
I'll have to contact you later.
Hmm? Trouble?
[MILLY] What are you doing
goofing off like that?
You're the festival chairman!
But everything
is running fine.
There's no problem!
Besides, you're taking
charge of that part, right?
It was two meters
wide up through last year,
then suddenly you declared
we had to have a 12-meter pizza!
[MILLY]
Uh huh! Isn't it great?
It's going to be the largest one
of its kind in the world!
[LELOUCH] Just the oven
and the ingredients
are causing an uproar.
And now there's a TV crew
running around campus?
You know we can't
show our faces!
[MILLY] But we have to
document making the pizza!
You can run things from
the control booth, okay?
President's orders.
[RIVALZ]
All right, stop right there!
[NINA] Rivalz!
We're all set on this end!
Wow, you're in a sunny mood.
Something good happen?
Yeah, you could say that!
[OHGI] Sorry, but an
Eleven from the ghetto
walking around alone would be--
[VILLETTA]
It's all right.
[OHGI] If you're afraid
that some Britannians, uh...
You needn't worry
about me so much.
I'm okay, really.
Anyway, is this going
to help you with your work?
[OHGI] Yes. I can gather data
for our development project.
I understand.
That's good, then.
[OHGI]
What the hell am I doing?
If I get the chance,
I should hand her over
to the cops or a hospital.
No, I can't.
If they connect me
to the Black Knights,
it would implicate everyone.
Even so, I can't just kill her!
I can't!
Here we are.
Is something wrong?
No, I used to be
a school teacher,
so I was feeling
a little nostalgic.
[VILLETTA]
Why did you stop teaching?
My best friend since
we were little kids...
Well, he's since passed on.
You could say that I'm living
out his dream in his place.
[OHGI] It's kind of a heavy
thing for me to carry around.
Let's go in.
[OHGI gasps]
No, I can't go into
a Britannian school!
I'm an Eleven!
[GIRL laughs]
That doesn't matter!
The campus is
open today! Come on!
Yeah, in you go, you two!
Wha--?
Hey, I found them first!
[SUZAKU]
That's a relief.
I thought you were never
going to come back to school.
It's on purpose?
Why didn't you tell anyone?
About who I really am?
[SUZAKU] You're Kallen Stadtfeld
right now, aren't you?
Not Kallen Kouzuki, right?
Are you trying to draw
me in by acting friendly?
On the battlefield,
I won't show any mercy.
But I want to try
to persuade you here.
I know this is
against the rules,
but while we're at school,
I'd rather try to
change your mind here
than defeat you in combat later.
[KALLEN gasps]
Something's different about you.
Suzaku, the truck's here.
The cheese--
You came back.
Uh, yeah.
I'm not as sick now, so...
Kallen, what we
were talking about
has nothing to do
with school, okay?
Yeah, I get it.
Kallen, if you don't mind,
could you go and
check in with your class?
They seem to be
a bit short-handed.
[KALLEN]
Sure, I don't mind.
I do mind!
[STUDENTS screaming]
Aw, this thing
actually scares them?
Ugh, I'm gonna
get Lelouch for this!
He should have told me
I had to be part
of the Horror House.
Hmph!
The only person I let
order me around is Zero!
[KALLEN] Oh great,
here comes another couple.
Why couldn't they make
this whole thing mechanical?
They've got this dumb screen...
It's sweltering inside of here!
It's like those early Glasgows.
Come on, move your ass!
Hurry! Move your ass!
[OHGI whimpering]
[KALLEN]
Ohgi?!
You're back safe?
Fortunately, yes.
[CECILE laughing]
School festivals are such fun!
I feel so free!
[CECILE laughing]
The one she keeps whacking--
doesn't he look like Lloyd?
No great wonder.
Working under that guy
must really drive her
out of her mind.
Right, the pizza
is starting later.
I definitely don't
have time to be doing this.
Yes. Oh, the drama club?
I've spoken to the
film club about it.
[LELOUCH] How can I
prepare my coup d'etat?
I'm sorry!
The handle just broke in two!
[LELOUCH] Soldiers?
How peaceful the world is...
Say, aren't you Suzaku's friend?
[C.C.]
Hey! You! Boy!
Where am I supposed
to go to eat the biggest pizza
in the world?
Oh, so you're here.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Good work getting them here
from Area 18 in one night.
Your forces are
impressive, Cornelia.
You flatter me.
I'm honored that you
deployed your regular
troops to fill in
for them, Schneizel.
[SCHNEIZEL]
It was the least I could do.
[CORNELIA]
The Glaston Knights,
who were standing by
in the homeland,
have joined us here,
and that means...
We even have Sattel
Waffe for the Gloucesters.
I understand.
And I'm going to play this card
in my negotiations
with the Chinese Federation.
[CORNELIA]
Please do.
What a great honor...
Being asked for assistance
by Princess Cornelia,
who is unmatched
on the battlefield.
Please, don't
tease me about this.
But I'm sincere.
On the field of combat,
you shine more beautifully
and brightly than any flower
or butterfly at a soirée.
Yes, like the Flash herself.
Please, stop saying that.
You know I'm only--
Now where could Euphy
have disappeared to?
I told her I was
coming to see you off.
I had a long talk
with Euphy last night.
[CORNELIA]
Last night?
Yes.
Ah, and about
the other matter?
Bartley's project?
Oh yes,
I really don't mind,
but will he actually
be of any use to us?
[C.C.] I'm asking about the
biggest pizza in the world.
[LELOUCH] I'll bring you some,
now wait in your room!
[C.C.] I don't believe you,
because you're a liar.
[LELOUCH] I'm not going
to deceive you over a pizza.
The military and
the press are here!
What if they see you?!
I'll wear a disguise.
I don't like cold pizza.
Right now,
I have a school festival
and a coup d'etat to run!
[KALLEN] Why did you
come into the school?
[VILLETTA]
Oh, that's my fault.
[KALLEN]
Who are you anyway?
You're definitely not an Eleven.
What's your name?
This is, uh... She's my...
[LELOUCH] Kallen?
Authorized personnel only.
Could you get them
out of here now?
[LELOUCH]
Ohgi?!
I'm really sorry,
but there's something I want
to talk to Suzaku about.
It's all right,
Your Highness.
Euphy, I think this
is a wonderful idea
you've come up with!
Really?! Then...?
You should follow
the path you believe in
with all your heart.
I'll discuss it with Cornelia
so that she understands.
[EUPHEMIA] Suzaku,
my brother approved my idea.
Now we can...
[gasps]
I'm so sorry!
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Are you okay?
Nunnally?!
Huh? That voice...
Is it you?
[KALLEN]
He's seen Ohgi now.
[LELOUCH]
This is bad.
If they see me here
with C.C., then...
[SHIRLEY] A propane tank
for the burner?
I'm sure the spare ones
are here, maybe in back.
[SHIRLEY]
Kallen?
Oh, hello. What's up?
Are there any spare
fuel tanks in the back there?
Rivalz needs one for the pizza.
[KALLEN] Uh, maybe
they're on the other side?
[SUZAKU]
Oh, okay.
Can this get
any more annoying?!
You can use
your Geass, can't you?
[LELOUCH] It'd be dangerous
to use it on Ohgi
and whoever that is with him.
And I've already used it
on everyone else here!
Well it's your own fault then.
You shouldn't use it so freely.
Your comments are not helping!
[SHIRLEY]
Is that Lelouch?
Are you here?
There's something important
I want to ask you about!
Find a way to
get out of here, fast!
Shirley. Can it wait?
I'm going to
create a diversion.
Use it to get away!
[SHIRLEY]
What are you talking about?
You're never around
in the first place.
[KALLEN shrieks]
[KALLEN] The panels
are falling! Run away!
[SHIRLEY screams]
Don't just stand there!
Watch out!
Uh, I... thank you.
I'm just glad you're okay.
But where'd all
the smoke come from?
It must be for
detecting gas leaks.
It looks like the main valve
was knocked loose.
Never mind that.
Can someone help me, please?
I'm in a little pain here.
What's the matter?
[SUZAKU]
My ankle.
It's a very familiar feeling.
[OHGI] Sorry you got caught
in that weirdness back there.
[VILLETTA] No.
It was actually sort of fun.
I haven't felt this excited
in a long time.
I think it's better
you move out of Area 11 now.
Whoever shot you
wouldn't come after you.
You should be safe.
Y'know, Ohgi,
I wonder if the person
I used to be
was as happy as I am now.
So, uh...
Can you tell me what
you were going to say
when we were back there
at the school?
[OHGI]
Uh...
You started with "She's my..."
She's my what?
Well you see...
[VILLETTA] I really don't think
I'd mind becoming an Eleven.
[NUNNALLY]
Will you keep our secret?
I mean about Lelouch
and I being here?
But if you just
stay here like this...
All I want is
to be with my brother.
That's all that matters.
Do you remember
that time when you and I
got into a great big argument?
On which of us was
going to marry Lelouch
when we grew up?
Yes, I do!
We put Lelouch on the spot
by making him decide
right then and there!
[BOTH laugh]
So how 'bout now?
[EUPHEMIA]
Huh?
Do you still love him?
Even to this day?
All right! Any moment!
We are about to
begin the historic task
of the making of the
world's largest pizza!
Please note that this
contraption at my feet
is an oven specially
built for this occasion!
A fabulous waste of money!
Yes, I understand, Shirley.
I promise I'll
make time for you.
Right now, just send group B
to the stage to help.
Right.
[LELOUCH]
This feels so easy!
If I make a mistake here,
no one's life is on the line.
Not bad.
Got everything on schedule, huh?
[LELOUCH] I've learned
to manage people lately.
Still, they seem
so optimistic, don't they?
The Chinese Federation
attacked just the other day,
yet look at everyone.
That's why we need this.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
Festivals are necessary.
For everyone, all the time.
You still need
to learn a bit more.
[laughs]
Okay, lesson learned!
[NUNNALLY]
Lelouch!
Nunnally, how's the pizza--
Sorry! I need a second!
Call me if something happens!
Huh?
It looks like the
ingredients are all prepared!
Now!
Introducing our
special dough tosser,
the Ashford family Ganymede!
[CROWD cheering]
[RIVALZ]
Yes, it's a bit of an antique.
However, at the controls is the
student council's
special member
and Princess Euphemia's personal
knight, Suzaku Kururugi!
[CROWD cheering]
Listen. Is that because of...?
Yes.
There are lots of
Elevens who came here today.
It's an open festival after all,
and this is Suzaku's school.
[KALLEN]
So they came to see him?
[SAYOKO] Yes. Suzaku's like
a ray of hope for many Elevens.
They revere him.
I see...
Ganymede, a third-generation
Knightmare...
The type used by
Lady Marianne the Flash,
isn't that correct?
It's just a fundamental frame.
A big puppet
for events like this.
An unorthodox design,
dropped for the next
generation of Knightmares
due to Lady Marianne's death.
I'm guessing
that's the real reason
you want to marry me.
So now you get it.
He has no attraction
whatsoever to the opposite sex.
[LLOYD] Well, I get
the general idea, anyway.
[RIVALZ]
And again!
Can he get it
any larger, folks?!
C'mon, Sir Suzaku!
We've got high hopes for you!
Last year,
it was my turn to do it,
but I can't compare
to a real pro.
This is a day
of sweet surprises.
To think you and Nunnally
were so close all this time...
And that you and Suzaku
are friends as well!
[SHIRLEY]
What is that guy doing?!
This is no time to be
hitting on some flirty girl!
I never want to see
people unhappy ever again.
Remember, we can't
meet after this.
That's not true.
I've found a solution
for everything.
Lelouch!
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
Is that Princess Euphemia?!
[CROWD gasping]
[GIRL]
Princess Euphemia?!
[RIVALZ]
What's up?
[CROWD chattering]
Princess Euphemia?!
Lelouch! Take Nunnally away!
[LELOUCH] Sorry to leave
you alone at a time like this.
That's right!
The sub-viceroy is
near the main entrance!
[BODYGUARD]
I copy!
I'll send in the back-up team!
Camera! Get a link
to the studio, quick!
All right!
Princess Euphemia's here!
No way! Why?
Where? Where is she?
Everyone stop! Don't run!
Please don't panic!
[C.C.]
Pizza...
Guess we should
have left this to the pros.
What do you think?
I'm afraid I'm just
going to have to give up
on this one.
And some other things.
[gunshots]
Everyone stop this at once!
Do you realize who this is?!
This is the Sub-Viceroy!
The Third Imperial Princess!
Thanks for your help.
We'll take over from here.
Stand back every--
HiTV! A comment!
Just one word, please!
Princess Euphemia,
it's me! Nina!
I'll get you out of here--
Ugh this is getting tight!
Please, excuse me!
No, don't!
You don't say?
Already? If you've
escaped on your own,
I'd say that's excellent,
Deputy Commander.
We'll stay right here.
Right.
Looks like we wasted
the equipment space
inside the news van.
There's no need for
the captain of the Zero squad
to escape now either.
I'd like you to continue
to stay undercover
here in the settlement.
I'll introduce you
to Zero later on.
I understand.
Oh, wow!
[CROWD exclaiming]
Princess Euphemia,
you're not hurt, are you?
I'm fine! Thank you, Suzaku!
Are you okay, Nunnally?
Yes. How about Euphemia?
She's all right.
Suzaku's taking care of her.
I see...
Lelouch, guess what?
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
Euphy said that
she and Suzaku
are becoming very close now.
[LELOUCH gasps]
They make a nice couple.
Don't you agree?
[LELOUCH]
Nunnally, you...
[EUPHEMIA] Thank heavens.
They're all right.
Princess Euphemia, down here,
can I get a statement, please?
[EUPHEMIA] Could you please
network this broadcast
nationwide?
Huh? You mean go live now?
Euphy?
I have a very
important announcement!
[DIETHARD]
Hm?
[GUILFORD] Your Highness!
It's Princess Euphemia!
[CORNELIA]
What's she doing now?
And we go to our
special live coverage!
I am Euphemia,
Sub-Viceroy of Area 11 of
the Holy Britannian Empire.
There is something
of great consequence
that I wish to
tell you all today!
Now what?
This little girl
makes such a fuss.
[EUPHEMIA]
I, Euphemia li Britannia,
hereby declare the formation
of the Specially
Administrated Zone of Japan
in the area
surrounding Mount Fuji!
What?! Britannia has...?!
They're recognizing Japan?!
[DIETHARD]
Dammit!
I never thought of this scheme.
Even though it's only
in a limited area...
Within the Specially
Administrated Zone of Japan,
Elevens will be permitted
to call themselves Japanese.
[EUPHEMIA]
Restrictions against Elevens
and special rights
for Britannians
will no longer
exist within this zone.
It will be a place where
Elevens and Britannians
live side by side as equals!
[LELOUCH]
Stop this, Euphy!
I already thought through
every detail of that scenario!
It's nothing but an empty dream!
[EUPHEMIA]
Do you hear me, Zero?!
[LELOUCH gasps]
I don't care about your past,
nor who you are
underneath that mask!
I beg you!
Join us in creating this
special zone of freedom!
Join Zero?
No way!
Just think about Prince Clovis!
[CORNELIA]
What is she doing?!
[EUPHEMIA] Zero, help me build
a new future within Britannia!
A place for everyone!
[CROWD cheering]
A Japanese zone?
Why's she doing that now?
That's pretty obvious.
She's in love with an Eleven.
[LELOUCH]
I'm finished.
Either way I go,
the Black Knights
will break apart over this!
The reason we exist
has vanished!
How could this
have happened so easily?!
You think you can just take it
all from me like this?!
Even if it is a place
where we can be ourselves...
You know nothing!
You understand nothing!
I am the terrorist
who hides his face.
And you...
[EUPHEMIA]
Lelouch!
Now it can be like before!
[LELOUCH] No, the past
is dead and gone!
Euphemia!
[LELOUCH] The Specially
Administrated Zone of Japan.
If I cooperate, I give up
the right to use force.
Oppose it, and the
people become my enemies,
and the Black Knights collapse.
Euphemia!
The third princess
who innocently holds
good intentions like a sword!
For Nunnally and me, your very
existence has become a crime!