[C.C.] The young
Britannian, Lelouch,
is faced with a choice
between two divergent paths.
One leads to the past
in a quest to find
his mother's enemies.
The other way takes him to
the future where he will create
a world in which his
little sister, Nunnally,
can live happily.
Only Lelouch can choose
which direction he will go.
Will he follow the path
that ends in destruction
of the world?
Or will he travel the road to
building a bright, new one?
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku...
I finally understand.
You...
[LELOUCH] Suzaku.
What Mao said...
Did you do it?
Did you kill your own father?
[gasps]
I see.
It's not just
your secret, is it?
Lelouch, I...
[LELOUCH]
Kirihara!
I think that was
the old man's name.
He claimed that Prime Minister
Genbu Kururugi killed himself
in order to stop all of
those in his cabinet
who called for
do-or-die resistance.
The story was a necessary one.
For Japan, and Britannia.
Thank you for that.
[LELOUCH] Frankly,
he's at odds with himself,
because he used to be different.
He never placed any
importance on another person.
It was tough enough for me
to kill my half brother...
Yet Suzaku killed his father
when he was only 10 years old...
He's been carrying that burden
around all these years?
[RIVALZ] C'mon, Lelouch,
quit moving around, will ya?
[LELOUCH gasps]
O-Oh, sorry, guys.
[RIVALZ] No, your
sight line was lower.
[LELOUCH]
Like this?
[RIVALZ]
Too far! Little higher!
[LELOUCH]
Good?
[RIVALZ groans]
Now your expression's
totally different
from when we started!
This was like this...
That went kinda like that...
And this was here...
There!
[GIRL ART A]
That's not how he was!
[GIRL ART B] I like
the frowny face more!
[RIVALZ] Come on, everyone!
I prefer him looking clueless.
Shirley, don't we have
math for first period?
Don't you remember?
It's Art Week?
Prince Clovis had
declared it that.
[CURATOR] We will open
Art Week with the dedication
of the Clovis Memorial
Museum of Art.
You, Princess Euphemia, will
select the First Place winner
from among these
submitted works.
[EUPHEMIA]
Oh, this one's nice.
I particularly
like this painting.
It's regrettable that
our investigation revealed
that the artist happens
to be one-quarter Eleven.
Perhaps it shouldn't
have been displayed here
in the first place, then.
[CURATOR] Well it's a delicate
balance with our public.
Anyway, take a look
at that painting right there.
It was painted by the
son of Marquess Nicolai.
[OHGI]
Octopus hotdogs...
Hmph. That girl...
[INOUE]
Excuse me...
No, these aren't
what you think!
[INOUE]
We have visitors.
They also have an
introduction from Kyoto.
You're the...
Four Holy Swords?!
I'll get straight
to the point here.
We've come to you today
to ask you for your help.
Uh, how do you mean?
Lt. Col. Tohdoh
has been apprehended.
He sacrificed himself
so that we could escape.
[LELOUCH]
I see. We'll help them.
You sure?
[LELOUCH] The Black Knights
fight for the cause of justice.
There's nothing odd about that.
[OHGI chuckles]
[GROUP sighs]
We'll use assembly
method B-13.
Take the sectioned
Knightmares via course 18.
You can have Diethard handle it.
Also alert those who are
to rendezvous with us.
Sorry I didn't meet with
the Chinese Federation.
Don't worry about it.
I've revised all
our plans with them.
Making any changes in
your usefulness to me
will only hinder the plan.
Besides, two chess pieces
I've been wanting
will be mine today.
And with any luck, a third...
[GUILFORD] Today, Kyoshiro
Tohdoh will be executed.
[CORNELIA]
I won't be present for that,
now that the Japan
Liberation Front is defunct.
[GUILFORD]
Right.
[CORNELIA]
No, wait.
Let him handle
the execution.
[EUPHEMIA]
Viceroy!
--[CORNELIA] Hm?
--[GUILFORD] Huh?
[CORNELIA] Sorry to
summon you like this.
How's everything at the museum?
The dedication is later on.
Of greater importance, though,
the N.A.C. reported there
was unrest in Ishikawa.
Probably backed by the E.U.
or the Chinese Federation.
And there have also been
sighting of Gun-Rus.
Still, it's our chance to
bring Hokuriku under control.
I'll leave Darlton
here while I'm gone.
If anything happens,
consult him.
Also, concerning what
we spoke of earlier...
[EUPHEMIA]
Huh?
[CORNELIA] You may choose any
one of them to be your knight.
They're all excellent soldiers
from respected families.
[NUNNALLY] Yes, the pond does
freeze solid in the winter.
Although, big brother
scolded me once
when he caught me skating on it.
[SUZAKU] We had a pond, too,
at the Kururugi shrine.
It was small, but I
used to catch zarigani--
I mean crawdads, all the time.
[NUNNALLY]
You would catch crawdads?
How?
It's simple.
You just tie a string
to a frog's back leg.
Huh? Frog, as in those things
that sit on lily pads
and go "croak!"?
Yeah, but in Japanese, they
go "kero-kero, kero-kero."
Huh? "Kero?"
--[SUZAKU] Yup. Kero-kero.
--[NUNNALLY laughs]
[LELOUCH] If things
continue at this pace
and keep proceeding
according to plan,
I won't be able to stay
with Nunnally any longer.
That affair with Mao
also drove home the fact
that I need someone to
protect my little sister.
Whoever that person will be,
if Nunnally's the one who gives
him a reason to live, then...
--[NUNNALLY laughs]
--Um? Lelouch?
I need to... tell you--
[CECILE]
Suzaku!
[LELOUCH]
Who's that?
She's a soldier.
Friends of yours?
Yes.
[CECILE]
I'm sorry,
but I need to pull Suzaku
away from you for a while.
Uh... but, um...
Don't worry,
I told you it's all right.
That guy isn't going
to come back here.
Right.
See you, then.
Please come again, Suzaku.
I will!
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
When you return,
there's something that
I want to... discuss.
It's an important matter.
Uh-oh.
I'm nervous.
I'll talk to you
when I get back.
Well, it seems that Suzaku's
really important to them.
I'm glad.
Nunnally, you seem...
fond of Suzaku.
Am I right?
I adore him.
But of course, I love you
more than anyone, Lelouch.
I see.
[SOPHIE]
Shirley, I'm gonna go on ahead.
[SHIRLEY] Oh, just
wait up, will ya?
Ah!
Oh, great...
Hm?
[REPORTER A] Sub-Viceroy, is it
true that no Eleven companies
were used in the construction
of this museum?
W-Well, with regard to
that question, I, uh...
We're looking into it right now,
so we have no answer
at this time.
Idiot!
Why bother asking princess
Euphemia about politics?!
[KERIMAN]
Keriman from Interstate.
Your Highness, there
have been rumors lately
that you're close to
choosing your knight.
Um... a knight.
Yes, well, you see I'm...
[CURATOR]
Ladies and gentlemen!
We ask that you please
limit your questions
to those concerning
the museum only.
[BK MEMBER A]
Hey, I heard from Brown Bear.
Salmon's group is moving in.
[BK MEMBER B] Gotcha. Tell
Ohgi it's too soon to reel...
[MINAMI] I told you not to
bunch up all the hydro lines
in one place!
[YOSHIDA] That's why I said it
was different from a Burai!
[ASAHINA] Are you sure
it's a good idea
to throw in with
the Black Knights?
[CHIBA] Can you think
of any other way
to rescue Col. Tohdoh?
[URABE] There's also
what Kyoto said,
that they would lend us
the new models.
Still, their principles
seem to be somewhat off.
We're not ethnocentric,
but after all, you
already know that.
We can worry
about the details
after we've rescued the colonel.
I understand.
But no matter where Tohdoh
may be, it's the place I belong.
[TAMAKI] Look, just stuff
'em in and close the lid,
for crying' out loud!
It's almost time to move out!
[RAKSHATA] Take your time, and
treat it with the utmost care!
[GROUP]
Huh?
It was far more fragile
than any of you
when I gave birth to it.
[TAMAKI] Huh?
Who the hell are you?!
I am its mother!
[ZERO]
You arrived on time.
Hm? Are you Zero?
It's a pleasure.
I've heard a lot of
things about you.
[ZERO] The pleasure
is all mine, Rakshata.
I've been reading about you
on the net for some time, now.
You have?
[ZERO] The articles relating
to medical cybernetics.
[chuckles] I do hate talking
about the past.
Anyway, here.
[ZERO]
Hm?
[RAKSHATA]
A souvenir from Kyoto.
[KALLEN]
Excuse me...
Is this really going to improve
the interfacing system?
[RAKSHATA]
No, of course not.
Huh?!
It's going to improve
your life expectancy.
I just heard they
changed your executioner.
It's going to be Warrant
Officer Suzaku Kururugi.
You oughta be glad
it's someone you know.
[LLOYD]
Wha...?
You need my signature again?
Even though Princess
Cornelia ordered this,
there are still some
formalities to be followed.
A change of executioner is
the most excepti
of circumstances.
[SUZAKU grunts]
[SUZAKU gasps]
What was that?
What happened?!
[LLOYD] Good, now we're free
of this hellish paperwork.
Colonel, we're
coming to save you.
These Gekkas are awesome!
Way superior to Burais!
Yeah! Ya got that right.
[RAKSHATA]
Hmm...
You think the sub-weaponry's
linkage isn't tight enough?
[TECH A] No. However,
I suspect it might be the line.
[TECH B] I'm reading
a 0.7 variance to specs.
[RAKSHATA] Obviously,
those old codgers in Kyoto
need to supply us
with better parts.
[INOUE]
Hm?
[SOLDIER A] My superiors have
just ordered that you be
unofficially executed before
you're busted out of here.
Any last words?
[TOHDOH] It's a life
I gave up once before.
It's worth nothing.
[ZERO] In that case,
I'll claim your life for myself.
What the hell?
[SOLDIER A screaming]
Zero!
[ZERO] Kyoshiro Tohdoh,
the only Japanese who,
seven years ago, brought
the mighty Britannian forces
to their knees in defeat.
You mean Itsukushima?
You want me to perform
a miracle for you, as well?
[ZERO]
That was no miracle.
It ended in victory
because it was based on
excellent intelligence work.
That's why I want you.
[TOHDOH] I pledged my loyalty
to General Katase.
Now that he's dead,
I wish to die, too.
[ZERO]
Don't be a coward!
What?
[ZERO] You must
take responsibility!
Responsibility for the
miracle that you made!
[ZERO] The Area 11
resistance movement
is more intense than that
of any other area because Japan
surrendered before exhausting
all of its military strength.
You failed to continue
the great hope
known as the Miracle
of Itsukushima!
You're saying it's my fault?
[ZERO]
Yes. People grasp at illusions
because they're
desperate for miracles.
Why else has there been
such rampant use of Refrain?
You must endeavor!
To the bitter end,
beyond all that's decent,
and then you can die!
Till the name of
Tohdoh the Miracle
has grown ragged and tattered!
You're telling me that
the Japanese people
can't accept their
defeat until then?
[ZERO] Till now,
they had to accept it.
However, now that
I'm here, there's hope,
because I can likely turn
their dreams into reality.
[TOHDOH]
Heh.
[CURATOR] And now for the
highlight of today's events.
Princess Euphemia will select
the grand prizewinner.
The work of art upon
which you place this flower
will be deemed the winner,
Your Highness.
[CHIBA]
Colonel!
Welcome back,
Col. Tohdoh!
Thank you.
You've all worked
so hard for this.
No effort at all, sir.
[TOHDOH]
Cooperate with Zero!
Eliminate the remaining
forces here!
[GROUP]
Roger!
[LELOUCH] Now all the tasks
at hand have been cleared.
And Nunnally's knight
has already been chosen.
That leaves only--
[gasps]
Damn!
What's he doing here?!
Well, how convenient.
The one problem left to contend
with has come here on his own!
[CURATOR]
Please, Your Highness,
it's time for you to decide.
We can't wait any longer.
I know, but I--
[EUPHEMIA]
But I...
[phone rings]
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
[REPORTER C]
Hello?
[multiple phones ring]
[REPORTERS]
Hello? Hello?
Escaped?!
They're skilled fighters!
[LLOYD]
Oh, my...
Aren't those new
enemy models amazing?
However, Ms. Cecile...
Yes?
In hindsight, it's certainly
quite fortunate that
the Lancelot's trailer is our
primary means of transport.
No, it's because you
spent our entire budget
on the Lancelot itself.
That's hindsight.
[RAKSHATA]
That's it?
The White Knightmare that's been
giving such trouble to Zero?
Uh, yeah.
[RAKSHATA]
Hm...
[REPORTER A] That's crazy!
One against seven?!
[REPORTER C] But that Lancelot
knightmare is holding its own!
[KERIMAN]
Whoa, he dodged it!
[REPORTER C]
Wow, and again!
[REPORTER A]
You show 'em, White Knight!
[DARLTON] Listen, send in
everything we've got.
Lend support to Kururugi,
then make them report that
we're wiping out the terrorists.
[TOHDOH] Zero, do you have any
data available on this unit?
[LELOUCH]
Possibly.
However, I want you to
do exactly as I say...
[TOHDOH] Ah. Very well.
I'll defer to you in this.
All units, give him distance!
[LELOUCH] Its speed
and maneuverability
are truly astonishing.
Nevertheless...
[LELOUCH] Its movements
follow a predictable pattern.
Its initial attack is
always straight on!
It never feints that first move.
[LELOUCH] Once you
dodge that attack,
he immediately moves
to avoid your offensive.
Check the data I'm sending you.
S-5-7!
[SUZAKU gasps]
Hey... He's really doing it.
[LELOUCH]
Right!
So now, the next move
he makes will be...
falling back to the rear!
Coordinates: X-2-3!
And with that...
...check!
[SUZAKU gasps]
I know this!
Who dares anticipate
my moves?!
No matter!
Dammit! It doesn't have
an ejection block on it!
What?! You mean we
didn't install one?!
[gasps] No way!
Is that really you, Suzaku?
What? Huh?
Zero! What now?!
Give us our next instructions!
Zero!
[LELOUCH] All this time,
it was him?!
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku!
[REPORTER A]
Hey, isn't that--?!
[REPORTER C]
Yeah. The Eleven.
[REPORTER D]
That's Suzaku Kururugi!
[KERIMAN] The one accused
of killing Prince Clovis?!
[REPORTER C]
They let an Eleven--
That's enough!
Turn off the monitor, now!
[EUPHEMIA]
Wait, please!
What?!
I'd like to watch
it to the end.
Good. I can still pilot.
Do not do this, Suzaku!
[gasps]
Col. Tohdoh!
So then. You want to live
more than you want to
follow your own principles?!
Do I disappoint you?
Very well, then keep to your
schedule and execute me!
[SUZAKU gasps]
But why?
Why are you there?
You can't be, because you...
...have to be by
Nunnally's side.
[TOHDOH]
What's wrong?
That's the reason
you're here, isn't it?!
You have become
a cowardly boy
who's afraid of altering
the status quo!
Denying everything in
our society is pointless!
Once I make them trust me,
I'll have the power
to change it!
[TOHDOH]
You're serious?!
I'm dead serious!
[TOHDOH] Then you must
continue down that path.
Huh?!
Regardless of whether
you win or lose,
you'll achieve nothing
unless you're prepared
to sacrifice everything!
And that goes for countries
as well as individuals!
Right!
[KALLEN] Zero, what do we do,
capture him or--Zero!
[SENBA] We're destroying the
White Knightmare! Got that?!
Wait for Zero's orders!
[CHIBA]
We're not waiting!
Captain Senba, take Spinning
Life-or-Death Formation!
[SENBA]
Roger!
[KALLEN]
Don't do it...!
No wait!
Stand down!
Don't worry.
It's a synchronized
4-way attack.
He'll never dodge it!
Kururugi, release the
harken booster, quickly!
The password is
my favorite food!
[CHIBA]
It can't...!
No way!
Huh?
Are you okay?!
Interesting fighting
style he uses!
This time, Asahina,
circle 'round to the left!
Stop it!
Zero!
We've done enough
fighting for now!
We achieved our
objective here!
Use escape route 3.
Withdraw immediately!
Mm?
An unwinnable battle's not
the same as a lost battle.
You seem to be well
aware of that, Zero.
Wait!
Now, releasing chaff smoke!
[REPORTER A]
Look, they're running!
[REPORTER C] He fought them
off?! The Black Knights?!
[EUPHEMIA]
Suzaku... well done.
[REPORTER C]
Damned traitor!
Why won't he follow them?!
[REPORTER D]
'Cuz they're Elevens, like him.
[KERIMAN]
Of course!
I thought 1 against 7 was
a bit much to swallow!
[DARLTON]
Hm? Princess Euphemia?
All of you!
I'll now answer the question
you asked me earlier!
You had inquired as
to whom I would select
to serve as my knight, correct?
[MUSEUM VISITORS mumbling]
The knight I have chosen
will be the young man
you see before you!
[EUPHEMIA] Warrant Officer
Suzaku Kururugi!
[MUSEUM VISITORS mumbling]
Tohdoh, I... I'm your--
I am your foe.
Hey, isn't Zero coming out?
[KALLEN] No. I called him,
but he won't answer.
[LELOUCH laughing]
What's wrong?
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku Kururugi.
Is he my enemy?
The man who I intended
to be Nunnally's protector
is now Euphemia's knight.
The Black Knights stand
ready for battle...
but am I ready for this?
Must I carry on regardless...
...so that I can reshape the
world into what I want it to be?