[NARRATOR]
Lelouch, a youth of Brittania,
had been granted
special abilities
by a mysterious girl.
Geass.
The power to command others.
To do absolutely anything.
And Lelouch is determined
to use that power
to bring the Britannian
Empire to its knees,
to avenge his mother,
and create a world
where his younger sister
Nunnally can find happiness.
All the while knowing
at the end of his quest,
the Britannian Emperor,
his father, awaits.
Or at least.
that was the hope Lelouch
carried in his heart back then.
[JEREMIAH] Do you know
anything about this weapon,
Suzaku Kururugi?
It was the one used to rob
Prince Clovis of his life.
The barrel striations
leave no doubt.
And we've done a little
homework on you as well.
You're the eldest child
of Japan's last acting Prime
Minister, are you not?
Your motive here is clear.
You're making a mistake.
I have never even
laid eyes on that gun.
We found your fingerprints
all over this weapon.
You're also suspected
of murdering members
of the royal guard.
Come clean now, and
you'll be judged as though
you were born a Britannian,
not some worthless Eleven.
You're wrong! I've done nothing!
[NUNNALLY] That was Suzaku
they mentioned on the news,
wasn't it?
[LELOUCH] Yep. It looks
like he's still alive.
[NUNNALLY]
Yeah.
It's been ages. We haven't seen
him since the war ended.
Even we...
And, Lelouch?
What is it?
It wasn't true what
the news said, was it?
Of course not.
Suzaku would never
do anything like that.
They've just made a mistake.
Yeah... Must be.
[LELOUCH] Right. Well...
Good night, Nunnally.
That's why we should've issued
a friggin' statement sooner!
We could've taken credit for it!
[OHGI sighs]
[OHGI] Naoto...
I'm not cut out for this.
I'm no leader...
[OWNER] Yes, everything
is just as you requested.
We have the best in
the business working on it.
Once the slide system
is in order, it's all yours.
Once I've erased
all of the evidence,
I should forget this
ever happened, right?
[HEADMASTER] Truly this has been
a painful incident for all.
The Viceroy of Area 11,
our beloved Prince Clovis,
has been lost to us forever.
However, we can and will bear
the weight of this tragedy.
And from this darkest
of hours, draw strength.
[LLOYD] We've lose the most
crucial part of the equation...
[CECILE]
Can we do it without him?
[LLOYD]
Don't I wish.
The other units never
let go of a good pilot.
And even if we got one, they'd
never match his readings...
His operational efficiciency
clocked in at 94%!
And you wanna replace him?
You should tell them that,
perhaps they'll let Suzaku go.
He's an honorary Britannian,
they'd never listen.
Ever since General
Bartley's disgrace,
the purebloods have the
military in an iron grip.
The purebloods what?
[LELOUCH]
Well, from what I understand,
they're saying that only
pureblood Britannians
should be allowed to
serve in the military.
[LLOYD]
Their view is,
one of their own can
never be a criminal.
But if the criminal
is an Eleven,
it paves the way for Margrave
Jeremiah to shut down
the practice of granting
natives Honorary status.
And what of Suzaku?
[LLOYD]
His fate's all but decided.
Hey, Lelouch, you got
anything goin' on later?
After all, classes have been
canceled for the day.
Folks have been
askin' for a rematch!
You are not gambling, you guys!
C'mon, don't be such
a stick in the mud.
She's right, though,
maybe it's time to quit.
Huh?!
I've found a better
opponent, actually.
You did? I don't get it?
You're cuttin' me in on
the action too, right?!
[LELOUCH laughing]
[LELOUCH] Better not.
It's not really up your alley.
[MUSEUM ANNOUNCER 1] Britannia's
resounding victory over Japan
opened the unenlightened
nation's eyes
to its true place
in today's world order.
Since then, the Empire
and Area 11
have walked hand in hand
down the road to revival.
[KALLEN] Sixteen hundred
hours at Tokyo Tower.
Why here of all places?
[SUGIYAMA] It was Kururugi
who contacted us, wasn't it?
[OHGI]
Hard to say.
Yeah, but he might
have been arrested
after his communciation
with Kallen.
Then we're in danger
here, we should go...
[HELP DESK ANNOUNCER]
Attention please.
Paging a Miss Kallen Stadtfeld
of Ashford Academy.
One of your personal effects
has been turned in
at the kiosk on the
observation deck. I repeat--
Hi, I'm assuming this
phone is yours, ma'am.
Um, something wrong,
it is yours, isn't it?
[KALLEN]
Uh-- Yeah. Thank you so much.
[OHGI]
Oh yeah, there's no debating it,
life is better here
thanks to Prince Clovis.
I mean, it's all
due to Britannia
that we could rebuild
as quickly as we did.
I'm happy about that...
[KALLEN]
Zero?
Um... Hello?
I want you to board the
outbound train on loop line 5.
And bring your friends.
[KALLEN]
What?!
You handled His Highness's
memorial program very well.
A little too weepy
for my tastes, but...
Yes, well, the masses
tend to like tearjerkers,
Your Excellency.
Spoken like a true TV man.
Still, I have to acknowledge
the finesse you've shown.
You did well in the
short time you had.
One would almost think
you were expecting
His Highness to meet
his untimely end.
[DIETHARD] It's quite common
for memorial programs
to be set in advance
for important people.
Does that include me as well?
[DIETHARD] Recent events may've
bumped you up the list a bit,
Your Excellency.
I wasn't deemed important
enough till now, is that it?
How forthright of you.
I'm afraid so, sir.
[JEREMIAH]
Ever thought of enlisting?
The army could use
more men like you.
I don't think it would
be a very good fit.
Not really my cup of tea.
You prefer the civil
sector, I take it?
No matter. I have another
favor to ask of you.
Tomorrow night, Suzaku Kururugi
will be transferred
to his court martial.
[DIETHARD] We should line
the road with good,
patriotic Britannians.
Excellent, you catch
on quickly, don't you?
Be sure the rabble
can see his face.
[VILLETTA]
Lord Jeremiah.
There are those
among the Elevens
who see Private
Kururugi as a hero.
Some might very well make
an attempt to free him.
I'll be there personally
aboard my Sutherland.
If anyone even thinks
of causing trouble,
they'll be executed
on the spot!
[TRAIN ANNOUNCER]
Attention, all passengers.
If you become aware of any
suspicious items onboard,
please alert metro personnel
by using the nearest...
What now?
[OHGI]
Uh.
[ZERO] Face forward
and look to your right.
What do you see?
[KALLEN]
The Britannian city.
It was stolen away from us...
and built on our sacrifice.
[ZERO]
And on the left?
[KALLEN]
I see our city.
Remants of a desiccated city
after the Britannians
sucked it dry.
[ZERO]
Good answer.
Now make your way to
the front of the train.
[TRAIN ANNOUNCER] The next stop
is Okubo. Okubo is next.
Those wishing to transfer
to the Chuo Soubu line
should exit at the next stop.
Okubo will be next.
Once again, those wishing to
transfer to the Chuo Soubu line
should exit at the next stop.
[gasps]
Was it you... on the phone?
[YOSHIDA] Whoa...
Do you think it's a trap?
[KALLEN]
Well? Was that you in Shinjuku?
Was that cease-fire your doing?
[SUGIYAMA]
Hey, we're talkin' to you!
[ALL gasp]
[ZERO] What do you think of
my tour of the settlement?
Your tour?
Aw, come on, there's no
way it was this joker.
[ZERO] I wanted you
to fully grasp the two.
The settlement...
And the ghetto.
Yeah, we know.
There's a difference
between us and them.
A very harsh one.
And that's why we resist them.
[ZERO]
You're wrong.
Britannia will not
fall to terrorism.
[OHGI]
Fall...?
[ZERO] It's little better
than childish nuisance.
[SUGIYAMA]
What was that?!
[YOSHIDA]
You callin' us a buncha kids?!
[ZERO]
You should know your enemy.
It is not people...
but Britannia itself!
It is a war you must wage,
but not on the innocent!
Take up your sword!
Fight for justice!
Heh... Oh, please.
That's all easy enough
to say, isn't it?!
Hiding behind that mask.
Why should we even trust you?!
[YOSHIDA]
She's right!
[SUGIYAMA]
Lose the mask!
[OHGI]
Right.
Are you going to show us
your face or not?
[ZERO]
Very well. I'll show you.
But rather than my face,
bear witness to my power.
If I deliver to you
the impossible,
then I might have
earned your trust.
[JAPANESE SOLDIER 1]
He killed a Prince of Britannia!
Suzaku Kururugi should
be treated as a hero!
[JAPANESE SOLDIER 2]
But he's an honorary Britannian!
[JAPANESE SOLDIER 3]
Prime Minister Kururugi
was his father!
[JAPANESE SOLDIER 4]
So what!
The bastard gave up Japan!
Our people don't know
that about him!
[MAJOR GENERAL]
The whole Shinjuku business
was the work of Kouzuki's
group, wasn't it?
Yes, sir, they're being led by
a man named Ohgi at the present.
[MAJOR GENERAL]
Hmm...
Has Kururugi's family
said anything?
No, sir, they broke contact with
him once he joined the military.
Tohdoh, what are
your thoughts?
We should not become involved
in this public execution.
[MAJOR GENERAL grunts]
That's cowardly.
You're Tohdoh the
Miracle Worker, right?
There is a difference between
miracles and foolhardiness.
Congratulations!
Those two you asked me about
weren't on the list
of casualties.
That's good to hear...
[LLOYD] Not much luck
on your end though.
You may be getting a trial,
but no one is pulling
for you, certainly.
[SUZAKU] But the courts are
where truth comes to light.
I expect there'll be more smoke
and mirrors than anything.
"The truth" is scarce of late...
[SUZAKU] If that's how
the world works, then...
...so be it. I've no regret.
[MALE REPORTER 1]
Any moment. Any moment now.
It's a sight to see.
The throngs lining the route.
All of them waiting
on bated breath.
Waiting for the accused murderer
of Prince Clovis to pass by.
Honoary Britannian, and former
Eleven, Suzaku Kururugi.
[DIETHARD]
Camera five's a little slow.
Talk to me, Charles.
Your team been deployed yet?
What? The studio? Let 'em wait.
Nothing's been pushed back,
everything's going
according to plan.
Here we go.
[MALE REPORTER 2]
I-I can see them!
They have the suspect!
Suzaku Kururugi is
headed this way!
Like clockwork.
Heh. What a circus this is.
And I'm as corrupt
as any of 'em.
[CROWD yelling]
[CECILE] This is insane. We
know that Suzaku is innocent.
[LLOYD] The court deemed
our testimony inadmissible.
There's nothing we can do.
Yes, but--
Is that altruism
or humanitarianism?
[CECILE] This isn't the time
for a game in semantics!
Not much else to do.
We both know where this
case is headed, don't we?
We couldn't reach
him at the summit.
All we can do is cut
our losses, really.
[MALE REPORTER 1] Voices of
scorn, growing ever louder.
Voices bearing testament to a
people's love of their prince.
Raining their judgment
down on a terrorist.
Suzaku!
[MALE REPORTER 1]
Margrave Jeremiah,
integral in settling this case,
will be presiding over
the trial as acting consul.
No way the three of 'em can
pull this off on their own.
[OHGI]
He told us...
He said he'd make
the impossible possible...
He gave his word...
to save Suzaku Kururugi.
[LELOUCH] Right. No need to
turn back. The die is cast.
[SOLDIER 1]
Acting Consul Jeremiah!
[JEREMIAH]
What is it?
[SOLDIER 1] Vehicle approaching
the main highway from Third.
We just let it through,
as you instructed, but...
Do you believe the target
could be a terrorist vehicle?
[SOLDIER 1]
Well, sir...
...it's Prince Clovis's car.
The prince's car?
Well, looks like
we've got a comedian.
Don't worry about it,
just let him through to us.
All forces, halt here!
Hey, they stopped,
they really did.
It's just a coincidence.
Yeah but he said Jerimiah would
try to hog all the limelight
and make some sort
of stand about it.
Coincidence!
[MALE REPORTER 1]
This is not a scheduled stop.
Could there have been
some sort of accident?
[MALE REPORTER 3]
This is site five.
There's a vehicle
approaching them.
[JEREMIAH]
Hmph.
[MALE REPORTER 4]
It's...
It's Prince Clovis's
personal transport!
And it's heading straight
for the cavalcade!
[OHGI] He's heading
straight at 'em...
What's he planning?
[KALLEN] Hope they can't
tell it's fake...
[ZERO]
I see. Just you two then.
[OHGI] I'm sorry, we just
need a little more time.
If more people
understood what we--
[ZERO] No, the two of
you will do just fine.
Come on, that's ridiculous,
there'll be too many of them!
[ZERO]
With your help,
clearing the task at hand
will be child's play.
I'll need this by tomorrow.
All that matters
is the exterior...
[JEREMIAH] You dare desecrate
His Highness' transport?!
Come out of there!
[JEREMIAH]
Huh?
[CROWD]
[ZERO]
I am...
...Zero!
Zero?
[MALE REPORTER 5]
Wh-Who is this person.
This man calling himself Zero,
standing before a full
military convoy?!
What is all this?
What the hell does
he think he's doin'?
[MALE REPORTER 1] Who is this
man calling himself Zero?!
[MALE REPORTER 1]
Ladies and gentleman...
Zero? Whaddya mean,
like "nothing"?
[MALE REPORTER 1]
Are we gazing on a terrorist?
Certainly not the wisest
if such is the case.
[SUZAKU]
Is he... an Eleven?
[LELOUCH] Now to return
the favor, Suzaku...
I've seen enough, Zero. This
little show of yours is over!
[gasps]
[JEREMIAH]
First things first.
Why don't you lose that mask?
What in the-?!
[VILLETTA] Lord Jeremiah,
be careful, he's got the--!
[LELOUCH]
Yes, Jeremiah...
You never saw inside this thing,
so you assume it
holds poison gas.
Wait, you don't understand-- Ah!
[MALE REPORTER 1] Can all of you
watching at home see this?
It's some sort of device,
although it's
purpose is unclear.
Stay with us, and we'll see
if this so-called terrorist
has anything to say.
You... bastard...
He's taken every
Britannian here hostage.
And he's done it without
them even knowing it!
[ZERO]
You intend to shoot?
I think you know
full well what...
Unit six, bring up the sound!
And get that camera
right in his face!
[CAMERAMAN]
Sir, it's too hairy out here.
[DIETHARD growls]
[DIETHARD]
Amateurs.
[JEREMIAH]
Fine.
What are your demands?
[ZERO]
An exchange. This for Kururugi.
[JEREMIAH]
Like hell!
He's charged with high treason
for murdering a prince!
I can't hand him over!
[ZERO] No.
You're mistaken, Jeremiah.
He's no murder...
[ZERO]
The man who killed Clovis...
...was myself!
[CROWD gasping]
Ah-ha.
Unbelievable!
The real culprit, eh?
[MALE REPORTER 1]
What? Wh-What does this mean?!
This masked man called Zero--
No, we can't be sure who he is.
But in any case...
...he claims to be
the real assassin!
So, where does this leave
the current suspect,
Private Kururugi?
Ah, crap, there's no
way outta this!
We are so screwed.
[ZERO]
For a single Eleven,
you'll save scores of
precious Britannians.
I find that to be a bargain.
[DIETHARD] This is all one
big performance to him!
He's mad, I tell you!
Disguising this truck
as His Highness's!
He'll pay the price
for mocking the crown!
[ZERO]
Careful.
You don't wish the public to
learn of "Orange," do you?
[JEREMIAH]
Huh?
[SOLDIER 1] Orange?
What's he talkin' about?
[SOLDIER 2]
I don't know.
[ZERO]
If I die, it'll all go public.
If you don't want
that to happen...
What are you talking
about? What is this?!
[ZERO] You'll do everything
in your power to let us go.
Your prisoner as well!
[JEREMIAH]
Right, understood.
You there, release the prisoner!
[gasps]
What on earth are
you doing, my lord?!
[JEREMIAH]
Get that man over here!
[VILLETTA]
Huh?!
[SOLDIER 1]
Should we?
[SOLDIER 2]
But...
Hand him over!
Nobody gets in his way!
No, what are you thinking?!
You can't do this!
[JEREMIAH]
Lord Kewell, this is an order!
[MALE REPORTER 1] It's hard to
tell what's happening from here,
but it seems that Kururugi's
release has been brokered!
[CROWD yelling]
So, who the hell are you-- Uh!
[ZERO] As I thought, they
didn't allow you to speak.
[VILLETTA] If they get away,
we'll lose everything!
It's time to go, Zero.
[ZERO]
Well then, till next time.
[CROWD screaming]
[VILLETTA]
You cowardly Eleven!
Lord Jeremiah,
what are you--?!
You heard me,
stand down, now!
They're not alone at all!
They jumped right off!
It worked! Now we can--
You imbecile! There's
nowhere for you to run!
[JEREMIAH]
Lord Kewell!
Are you going to
follow orders or not?!
And believe me, there
will be repercussions.
All units, do I
make myself clear?!
Do everything in your power
to help them get away!
[SUGIYAMA] Man... I didn't
really think he could do it.
[MINAMI]
Yeah, who is this guy?
[TAMAKI]
That's crap!
How many times can a bluff
like that work, anyway?
[OHGI] Ya gotta give the
guy some credit, though.
[TAMAKI]
Huh?
Gotta admit it, nobody else
could 'a pulled that off.
Not the Japanese
Liberation Front.
Certainly not me.
We've always thought that
a full on war with Britannia
wasn't a possibility at all.
But maybe with him... it is.
[ZERO] It looks like they
treated you rather roughly.
Now you know what they're
really like, Private Kururugi.
Britannia is rotten.
If you wish to bring change
to this world, then join me.
So is it true?
Are you really the one
who killed Prince Clovis?
[ZERO]
This is war.
Why wouldn't I kill
an enemy commander?
And the gas? Those were
civilians out there!
[ZERO]
A bluff. To help things along.
The result: Not a single death.
[SUZAKU]
The result?
That's all that matters
to you, I suppose.
Hmph.
[ZERO]
Come, join me.
The Britannia you serve
is a worthless dominion.
[SUZAKU]
Maybe that's true. But...
But this nation, it can
be changed for the better.
And from within.
[ZERO]
Changed?
[SUZAKU] And any ends gained
through contemptible means
aren't worth anything.
[ZERO]
Wait! Where are you going?!
[SUZAKU] My court
martial begins in an hour.
[ZERO grunts]
[ZERO]
Are you mad?!
The only reason they're
giving you a trial
is to find you guilty!
The judge, the prosecution,
and defense!
[SUZAKU]
Rules are rules.
And if I don't go,
they'll start cracking down
on Elevens and
Honorary Britannians.
[ZERO]
But you'll die!
I don't mind.
[ZERO]
Don't be an idiot!
An old friend of mine
always used to tell me that.
He'd say I was a fool...
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
It's my weakness, I guess.
I'd try to bring you in, but
you'd just end up killing me.
And if I'm going to die, it'll
be in the service of the people.
Even so. I thank you.
For saving me.
[LELOUCH]
You... fool!
[NEWS RADIO MAN 1]
Yes, apparently.
Private Kururugi has made
conatct with the authorities.
It would seem this
Zero has released him.
[NEWS RADIO MAN 2]
However,
now that the original
charges against him
have been thrown into question,
it's very possible Kururugi will
be found innocent and acquited.
Thank goodness.
[door opens]
Miss Sayoko?
[LELOUCH]
So naive...
I was sure Suzaku
would understand.
Change the system from within?
Ridiculous!
The system will just
swallow him up!
It'll eat him alive!
I can't beg for their
charity to live my life.
I just can't! I won't live
by their "rules" anymore!