[C.C.]
Imperial Calendar, 2018.
As the Holy Britannian
Empire continues its drive
to dominate the world,
a lone rebel is resurrected.
His name is Zero.
A mysterious girl named
C.C. has given him
the power of Geass,
the absolute power
to compel anyone to obey him.
Now, Zero is again
challenging the Britannian
conquerors of Japan,
the once proud nation
now referred to only as Area 11.
As his actions spread like
a ripple through the world,
how will they affect
the people of this age?
For the moment, no one knows.
[G1 OFFICER 1]
What about the O.S.I.
forces that broke in first?
[G1 OFFICER 2]
No contact with them yet.
[G1 OFFICER 1]
The chaff density should
be dropping now.
Recon section four!
[G1 OFFICER 3]
The terrorists remain embattled
inside of Babel Tower.
They're believed to be members
of the Black Knights
We've confirmed the presence
of enemy Knightmare Frames.
[G1 OFFICER 1]
All right, Special Weapons
Batallion Seven will
break in from below.
[PILOTS]
Yes, my lord!
[BLACK KNIGHT] This is
hopeless! Let's run for it!
Just hold out
a little bit longer.
Wait until Zero can get the
layout of the building!
We'll back you up,
but you've gotta stand firm!
[KALLEN]
Lelouch...
It's true, I am Zero.
[gasps] Zero!
It's Lelouch!
It's the man who's used
the Japanese people!
Who's used you!
You wanna defend a
man like that?! You?!
[gasps]
[groans]
[LELOUCH]
Hm.
Zero, this is the end of you.
[LELOUCH] I was defeated
by the old me. By Suzaku.
And by my biggest enemy.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH]
He dragged me before
the Britannian Emperor!
[groans]
[EMPEROR]
The former 17th heir
to the imperial throne,
Lelouch vi Britannia.
It's been a long time,
hasn't it, my errant son?
How dare you!
You won't use your Geass!
Your Majesty, I have a request.
Please, sire, allow me to join
the Knights of the Round,
the 12 strongest knights
of the Britannian empire!
As a reward for capturing
Zero, is that it?
[LELOUCH]
You!
[SUZAKU]
I told you before, Lelouch,
that I was going to change
this world from the inside.
[LELOUCH] Even if it means
selling out your friends?!
That's right.
[LELOUCH]
Tch!
Very well.
I like the answer
you just gave him.
Now then, as a
Knight of the Round,
I order you: Cover up
Zero's left eye.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[EMPEROR] My unworthy son,
who raised the banner
of rebellion although
he was a prince.
Still, there's another way
we can make use of him.
What?!
[EMPEROR]
I will rewrite your memory:
About being Zero, about
the death of your mother,
about the very
existence of Nunnally...
[LELOUCH]
No! Geass?!
[EMPEROR]
You'll remember none of it.
You'll just be insignificant.
No, stop!
You're stealing what's
most precious to me again!
First my mother, and now
you're taking Nunnally?!
[EMPEROR] Charles zi Britannia
engraves into you...
Stop it!
False memories of a false life.
[screaming]
C.C...
Don't even think it.
I'm not the one who
gave him his Geass.
[LELOUCH]
Hm.
Where is Nunnally now?
[C.C.]
We tried to find your sister,
but with the Black Knights
all but destroyed,
that's why--
[LELOUCH]
What about Sayoko?
[C.C.]
She and Diethard escaped
to the Chinese Federation.
She still doesn't know
Zero's true identity.
And she didn't know
Nunnally's real importance,
so she can't be blamed.
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
I'll find the one
who gave the emperor
his Geass and then get Nunnally.
[LELOUCH gasps]
I had a younger sister,
but not a younger brother!
So, who is he?
[gasps]
[ROLO]
Thank goodness!
You're Britannian
soldiers, right?
I'm looking for my big brother.
This has the layout
of the building
in detail, but the I.D.
code I need isn't here.
So we can't commandeer
this Knightmare, can we?
[KNIGHTMARE 1]
What are you doing there?
That's a student
uniform, isn't it?
Oh, you're a soldier!
Thank goodness!
We need to help
this man at once!
Office of Secret Intelligence?
What are the emperor's
personal agents doing here?
[LELOUCH] Good. These
reports are accurate.
Calares's forces
don't know about me.
So I can use the data
in this journal.
There's only one survivor?
Yes. Just you.
What?
[LELOUCH]
That's right.
Now give me your Knightmare.
I understand.
The I.D. code is QR5-YK1D6.
[LELOUCH]
Thank you.
Even though you need
direct eye contact,
are those theatrics necessary?
[LELOUCH]
I don't need comments
from an immortal witch.
[chuckles]
[CALARES] The terrorists are
staging a counterattack?
[GUILFORD]
Yes.
It seems that they've managed
to capture some
of our Knightmares.
That's disgraceful!
Still, their numbers are small.
If I could possibly
join the battle...
[CALARES]
No.
You're still a guest here,
and under our protection.
As viceroy, it's my
place to go out there.
[GUILFORD]
But...
[GAO HAI]
Hm...
I don't like the spices
in Chinese food.
However, I might enjoy it.
Huh?
[CALARES]
A manhunt.
[ELEVENS yelling]
Let me see you
burst, Britannian!
Well done, Q1! Now,
head up to level 21.
P4, block the stairway.
R5, left 30 degrees.
N1, fire a barrage
50 meters ahead,
angled toward the ceiling.
[G1 OFFICER 4]
Contact lost with Lord Emilio!
[G1 OFFICER 2]
Change I.F.F. codes!
[G1 OFFICER 3]
We have! Five times already!
[G1 OFFICER 4]
Ortiz unit, wiped out!
[G1 OFFICER 1]
Outrageous!
Who's directing
these terrorists?!
[CALARES]
What are you doing?
Viceroy!
So, Zero really is
just a student, huh?
Well, he's something special!
[BLACK KNIGHT 1] Zero supplied
more stolen Sutherlands
for us to use.
Get on them, fast!
[BLACK KNIGHT 2]
With Zero here, we can win!
[BLACK KIGHT 3] He'll make
a miracle for us! He will!
Damned terrorists!
[LELOUCH chuckles] Shouldn't
Viceroy Calares be making
his appearance, soon?
[KALLEN]
It's going well.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
Kallen I sent
you to level 21.
I wanted to be
here by your side.
We're finally alone,
just you and me.
It would seem that somebody
is nibbling at the bait
we left in Area 11.
Is it C.C., Majesty?
We do not know that.
Kururugi, even among
Knights of the Round,
you're the first one
ever allowed to
enter this place.
Even Schneizel and the
others aren't aware of it.
[SUZAKU] I'm honored,
Your Majesty. But, why me?
[EMPEROR]
Because you are the only one
of the Knights of
the Round who knows...
[gasps]
About Zero's
identity. And Geass.
[gasps]
This place... Is it a shrine?
[EMPEROR]
No, it's not.
This is...
This is a weapon
for destroying God.
[SUZAKU]
A weapon?!
It is called the
Sword of Akasha.
[LELOUCH] You, who abandoned
Zero at Kamine Island,
what do you wanna tell me?
Lelouch, you were deceiving me
right from the very beginning.
[LELOUCH] About Zero
being your classmate?
Or about my Geass power?
Which one has offended you?
Both of them.
Tell me this!
Did you use your Geass on me
like you did the others?
Did you twist my
mind and my heart
and make me follow you?
[LELOUCH laughs]
Lelouch!
Your mind and your heart
are yours alone.
As was your loyalty
and admiration for Zero.
[KALLEN]
Don't move!
[LELOUCH]
Kallen, you should be proud
of what you did. You decided.
You made the choice.
You chose...
...Zero.
[grunts]
You don't believe me?
I wanted to believe so much
that I'd become a slave...
I see.
But the one that I
believe in is Zero!
Just him! It's not you, Lelouch!
[LELOUCH] Well, fine
with me. By the way...
Are you ever going to change
out of those clothes?
[gasps]
Don't look at me, you pervert!
Oh? Is that the way
you talk to Zero now?
[KALLEN]
I'm saying it to you, Lelouch!
Very well then.
[beeping]
Go ahead.
Britannian reinforcements
are here.
[BLACK KNIGHT 4] There's
zillions of 'em! What do we do?
[BLACK KNIGHT 5]
We can't beat this many!
There's no chance.
What's happening over there?
[G1 OFFICER 1]
Special Weapons Batallion Four
has begun to drop.
[CALARES]
Show the Chinese Federation!
Show them our emperor's might!
The overwhelming power of
our Holy Britannian Empire!
[G1 OFFICERS]
Yes, my lord!
They're coming in
from above, too!
[LELOUCH]
That's right.
[KALLEN gasps]
Viceroy Calares
must have arrived.
Escape would be
difficult. That's why...
...I'm going to win.
[G1 OFFICER 1]
Assault team two now has control
up to floor J!
[G1 OFFICER 2] That leaves
only one escape route
the Black Knights can use.
[CALARES]
And our main fighting force
is right there waiting for them.
Yes, sir.
We just need to drive them out.
Set up a broadcast link quickly.
We'll make the extermination
of these terrorists
a media event.
The Britannians must feel
certain of their victory.
That clears all
the tasks at hand.
All that's left is
your level, right?
[C.C.] We'll be finished
in ten minutes.
[LELOUCH]
Understood.
We'll make a stand
here to buy you time.
What about Diethard's setup?
[LELOUCH]
The system's still running.
Everything is going
according to plan.
[BLACK KNIGHT 6]
This is B2!
A single enemy
Knightmare is-- Agh!
What's wrong?
[BLACK KNIGHT 6]
But, that's-- It was just there!
B2? What's going on?
An enemy deactivating his
I.F.F.? Operating on his own?
[BLACK KNIGHT 7] Zero, this is
P6! The enemy is...! It's-- Agh!
[LELOUCH]
P6!
[BLACK KNIGHT 7]
This is R5! They destroyed R1!
[LELOUCH]
This isn't good.
And he's headed right for me!
[URABE]
Zero!
At the very least, you
have to get outta here!
We can move in
and act as decoys,
sacrificial pawns for
the plan. So, please...
[LELOUCH]
That's wrong.
[URABE]
Hm?
[LELOUCH]
You're mistaken, Urabe.
If you consider
yourselves disposable,
you'll never beat
the Britannians.
[KALLEN gasps]
[BLACK KNGIHT 8]
Captain Urabe!
Can you get over there?
[BLACK KNIGHT 8]
Yeah.
The cargo loading dock, right?
[URABE]
Yes.
It's a shortcut to this level.
[BLACK KNGIHT 8]
Confirmed.
[BLACK KNIGHT 8]
Yes, I see it.
This looks like a
mass-production prototype
based on the Lancelot.
[LELOUCH]
I see.
Still, this is not the
time to try capturing it.
Destroy it.
[BLACK KNIGHT 8]
Understood.
Huh?
It vanished?!
[BLACK KNIGHT 8]
How'd it get over here?!
Hold on!
Are you saying the
Knightmare "disappeared?!"
C.C.!
Aren't you finished
preparing that level yet?
Why are you panicking?
You have Kallen
and Urabe with you.
[LELOUCH gasps]
That's it! The aberration!
[LELOUCH]
You're out of your league.
You aren't Suzaku,
and your maneuvers
are no match for real strategy.
We've got the advantage
in close-range combat!
[URABE]
Too slow!
It vanished! Just like that!
Fast as a god!
[LELOUCH]
That can't be...
It's not physically possible!
It must be something else!
[LELOUCH]
It's closing in!
Urabe!
[KALLEN]
Oh, no!
[URABE] Zero, I don't care
if you're really a student,
or what your background is.
And I know you meant
it when you said
we're not expendable.
I know that every fighter
we've got counts.
Kozuki!
Ye-Yes?
[URABE]
Protect Zero.
He's our last hope, and hope
is what our people need.
Forgive me, Rakshata.
[URABE]
Zero! Save Japan!
Help our people to lift
their heads again and fight!
"The Four Holy Swords"...
...have proven our worth.
Urabe...
[beeping]
[LELOUCH]
Damn.
He used that
teleportation again.
No, wait!
[KALLEN]
I have to make my move now.
This one's for Zero.
I have more bad news for you.
We're all finished here.
Then it's done.
Urabe, your sacrifice
wasn't in vain.
Hope begins now!
[CALARES] Damned terrorists!
A suicide attack!
Uncivilized monkeys!
[G1 OFFICER 4]
All units, lost!
Contact lost with all units!
--[KNIGHTMARE 3] Wh-What the--?!
--[KNIGHTMARE 4 screams]
[PILOT 2]
Ascending from intercept
to 1,500 and circling!
[KALLEN]
That's it!
The tower will smash
the enemies above us
and crush them as it falls!
[LELOUCH]
Not just that.
[gasps]
No! It can't be!
[LELOUCH]
Your mistake was sealing off
your escape route.
And signaling your location
like that made you
so easy to target.
[CALARES screams]
[laughs] Goodbye,
Viceroy Calares.
[BUREAU A]
The viceroy has been killed?!
[BUREAU B]
Where's Lord Cornwell?
[BUREAU A]
He was with the viceroy.
[BUREAU B] Then, who's next
in the chain of command?
[BUREAU A] The Minister
of Internal Affairs.
[BUREAU B]
A civil servant in charge now?!
This is no time to panic!
[BUREAU A, BUREAU B]
Hm?
[GUILFORD]
I am taking command!
This is not a grab
for political power!
It's a temporary measure!
I swear it in the
name of my princess!
I ask for your cooperation!
The Princess?
[BUREAU B]
Does he mean Princess Cornelia?
In that case...
[BUREAU B]
Right.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, my lord!
[GUILFORD]
Thank you. I am grateful to you.
Now then, I'll go to the scene
to direct emergency
rescue operations.
Alfred, you contact the police.
Bart, you remain here.
[BART, ALFRED gasp]
[GUILFORD]
Hm?
[gasps] But that's...!
What's wrong?
[ZERO]
I am Zero!
What the hell?!
[gasps]
[MAN]
Whoa, whoa! What the--?!
[WOMAN]
Isn't that Zero?
[MAN 2]
No...
[MAN 3]
I thought he was dead!
[ONLOOKER]
How could this happen?
[GIRL] It can't be
the real Zero, can it?
[ZERO] People of Japan,
I have returned!
Kill the video!
I can't! It won't
take my access code!
[DIETHARD] That's it!
The Omega Line that I set up!
And the only one
who knows about it...
...is Zero!
Yes! I knew you
were still alive!
[ZERO]
Hear me, Britannia!
All you who have power,
heed my words carefully.
I am burdened by sorrow.
[gasps]
[ZERO]
War and discrimination.
Malicious deeds carried
out by the strong.
The same abhorrent interplay
of tragedy and comedy.
The world has not changed!
The people still suffer.
That is why the resurrection
of Zero was necessary!
So long as the strong
oppress the weak,
my rebellion will
continue to grow!
It begins today with
the divine punishment
I have wrought upon the inept
and foolish Viceroy Calares!
Man, oh man.
The Elevens' rebel
leader sure popped
back up with a vengeance.
Right, Suzaku?
Got it! The signal's coming from
the Chinese
Federation consulate!
Chinese Federation?
Has he defected?
They broke through
our encirclement.
[gasps] Of course!
They've stayed inside
the fallen building!
They've made Babel Tower
itself their pathway!
But, what about the
Chinese Federation?
Did they plan this out
with them beforehand?
Is that possible?!
C'mon, Zero's dead, isn't he?
Yes.
So, this guy's a fake.
And whoever he is,
if we just go over there
and storm the consulate...
Then we'd be breaking our treaty
with them, risking an
international incident.
He's saying that he's Zero,
and Zero killed our royals.
That gives this equal
status with the E.U. war.
It's a slippery
slope, either way.
[KALLEN]
Killing the viceroy and securing
our escape route.
He was able to do
both at the same time!
[XING-KE] Such cunning and
audacity is impressive.
It's Zero! The real one!
[ZERO]
I shall fight against all those
who abuse their power!
[ZERO] Therefore, once
again, here and now,
I declare the establishment
of the United States of Japan!
Are you certain about this?
We still haven't
received direct orders
from the Empress.
Are you dissatisfied
with my decision?
No. Never mind.
[laughs] Zero, you've actually
founded the United States of...
...Japan.
[VILETTA]
Terrorists forming a nation?
[ZERO]
Starting from this moment,
this room shall be the first
dominion of the U.S.J.!
[laughs] A nation consisting
of just one room!
That man's as amusing as ever.
[ZERO] Race, ideology, and
religion will not matter!
Being a citizen will have
but one requirement!
To do that which is just!
I trust you understand
the consequences
if you force your way in.
All right.
We'll settle this in
diplomatic chambers later.
[XING-KE]
Zero...
How useful will he
prove to us in the end?
[gasps]
If you're Britannian,
you have already
been asked to leave.
Or, are you one of
Zero's followers?
[ROLO]
I'm not sure. Which am I?
I'm not terribly
fond of riddles.
[ROLO] Yes, I'm exactly
the same way, myself.
What I wanna
know is the truth.
That's why I came
here to kill Zero.
[LELOUCH] I cannot move
a world by waiting.
To find Nunnally
and get her back,
I'm going to need real power.
Power stronger than
the emperor and Suzaku.
I must seize that power,
and I'll use my Geass to do it!
With the United States of Japan
as my starting point,
I'll build a new world
that's even greater
than Britannia.
But before I can do it,
I'll need to take care of him
My phony little brother, Rolo.