[CORNELIA]
I see...
So you were Zero...
...the entire time.
[CORNELIA]
Darlton was right.
He said it was
someone with a grudge
against the Britannian
imperial family.
Y-You did this... for Nunnally?
[LELOUCH]
Correct.
I will demolish
the present world,
then build a new and
better one in its place.
[CORNELIA] You killed them all
for the sake of that madness?!
Clovis?
Even Euphy?!
You're one to talk,
my dear sister,
considering how you idolized
my mother, Marianne the Flash.
It would seem... that
talking with you further...
...will prove to be
utterly pointless.
Indeed.
Well then...
Lelouch vi Britannia
orders you to answer him!
Go on.
[LELOUCH] Sister, are you
the one who killed my mother?
I'm not.
[LELOUCH]
Then who was it?
I don't know.
[LELOUCH gasps]
But you were put in charge
of her personal guard,
were you not?!
[CORNELIA]
Yes.
[LELOUCH] Then why did
you withdraw her escort?
[CORNELIA]
I was asked to.
[LELOUCH]
By whom?!
[CORNELIA]
Lady Marianne.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Mother did?!
That's impossible!
My mother knew she would
be attacked that day?!
No... That can't be!
If she did, she would have
gotten us out of there!
What really happened back then?!
Who killed her?!
Who killed my mother, dammit?!
[CORNELIA]
Uh...
[LELOUCH]
You don't know the truth?!
Then who does?!
Someone must know!
You, yourself, investigated
what occurred that day!
[CORNELIA] I remember
His Majesty the Emperor
ordered Schneizel to transport
the body out of there.
[LELOUCH]
The body?
You mean Mother's?!
Then... what was in that coffin?
[C.C. gasps]
Hey, get back in here!
[LELOUCH] I know! The government
bureau's defense forces
will be here soon.
[C.C.] No! Your little
sister's been kidnapped!
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
C.C., this is not
the time for jokes!
We'll take Cornelia back to the
command center as our hostage.
She's been taken!
I just know because
she's the reason you live!
She's on Kamine Island!
[LELOUCH]
Kamine Island?
[JEREMIAH]
All hail Britannia!
Mr. Zero?! Can it really be?!
What?! Oh, what luck! What fate!
What evil fortune!
[ZERO]
Is that you, Orange Boy?
Oh! Ohh! I beseech you!
I'm begging you, please die!
[LELOUCH]
Damn! Get Cornelia!
I'm already on it!
[CORNELIA groans]
[ZERO groans]
[JEREMIAH]
Zero!
I...
...must rid the world
of the empire's enemies!
Yes! And so...
All hail Britannia!
It's a damn disgrace!
If we report to the prince
what happened here...
[RESEARCHER A] It's only
his emotions running wild.
His behavior's too hard
to predict right now!
[BARTLEY] I wish we could
communicate with him!
Get through to him somehow!
[growls] Out of the way!
[JEREMIAH]
Zero!
[COMM] Currently passing
through Ozuite Area...
[CECILE]
Why did you try to stop Suzaku?
[LLOYD]
I'm a military contractor.
[CECILE] You didn't want
him killed, did you?
[LLOYD]
Why should I care?
You know as well as I do...
[CECILE]
Uh?
[LLOYD]
The biggest human flaw is that
we're so pitifully fragile--
in our bodies, our hearts,
and our relationships
with each other.
[CECILE] Nevertheless,
you can't bend the world
or people any
which way you want.
[LLOYD] I want every
part in my mechanisms
to function exactly as I wish.
If we lose Kururugi, we'll just
have to find another Devicer.
Be careful, please!
Any Knightmare
entering the field
will shut down immediately.
[BURAI PILOT]
Understood.
[SUZAKU gasps, growls]
[JEREMIAH]
Hmph!
He's very good.
Ohgi, it's Zero.
[MINAMI]
Zero! Thank god!
[LELOUCH]
Hm? What?
Minami, where's Ohgi?
Someone shot him!
We're treating him,
but he's unconscious.
And the culprit who
shot him is still--
[LELOUCH]
All right, you'll do.
The girl in the wheelchair-- do
you know where she is right now?
[MINAMI]
Uh... Isn't Ohgi more important?
[LELOUCH] I'll arrange
for his replacement later!
The girl in the
wheelchair comes first!
His replacement?!
[LELOUCH]
Confirm her location! Hurry!
All of the students we had
confined alone have disappeared.
In the confusion
when Ohgi was shot--
[STAFF]
Bring as many as you can.
Medicine, too.
Hang in there, Ohgi!
--[phone rings]
--[RIVALZ] Lelouch!
This is a bad time.
[LELOUCH]
Is Nunnally there with you?
[RIVALZ]
No, she's in the clubhouse.
We're just a
short distance away.
[LELOUCH]
Understood!
--[phone clicks]
--[RIVALZ] No! Wait!
Hey, where are you, anyway?!
--[gun cocks]
--[ALL gasp]
Damn, I can't get through
to Nunnally or even Sayoko!
Lelouch, you know I'm here
with you as your accomplice.
But also as your ally.
[LELOUCH]
So I should trust you?
Take the word of a woman who
won't give me any reasons?
Look, I don't want you to die.
At least that's true.
[LELOUCH] Hmph. That's just
a one-sided convenience!
Third Squad, enemy aircraft!
Sync fire and shoot it down!
[KAGEZAKI]
Roger!
Tracking enemy... Fire!
[JEREMIAH growls]
[JEREMIAH]
I see them...!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
[SUBORDINATE]
Captain Kagezaki...!
[JEREMIAH]
Zero! Zero!
That's it!
I don't have time to fool
with cannon fodder like you!
C.C.! Get to 12th Street now!
Talk about one-sided
convenience!
[JEREMIAH]
You missed!
You can't hit me...
Jeremiah Gottwald!
You're wrong, Orange Boy.
You're being hit right now.
Coward! Behind from back?!
[LELOUCH]
Be crushed to dust, you relic!
All right...
Now to get Nunnally.
[grunts]
[SUZAKU grunts]
[TAMAKI]
Damn, that's a thick hatch!
Wish we had the sword
with the rotating blade.
[STAFF T]
Tamaki!
What do you want us
to do with them?
Should we lock
them in the dorms
or the gym with
the other students?
Students?
[SHIRLEY]
Call Zero!
[SUZAKU gasps]
[TAMAKI growls]
I guarantee you that
Zero wants us to be safe!
If not, something's wrong!
He's trying to guard us!
Aw, shut up!
Zero and me, we're tight,
and I know the man
better than anybody!
And he's not gonna
hesitate to shoot anyone
at a time like this!
--[SUZAKU] Stop!
--[TAMAKI] Huh?
[TAMAKI]
Ho! What's this?
The Japanese knight comes
out to help the Brits, huh?
Suzaku...
That white Knightmare is
all we came here to get.
A dirty traitor like you
can die right there!
--[ARTHUR screeches]
--[TAMAKI screams]
[ARTHUR hisses]
Arthur!
Stupid ass cat! Screw this,
just kill all of 'em!
[All gasp]
[LLOYD]
Good evening, everyone!
[SUZAKU]
Huh?!
[STAFF T2]
Retreat! Let's pull out!
[RAKSHATA gasps]
You're kidding!
That Earl of Pudding actually
came out to the front lines?!
[LLOYD] Rakshata...
I thought it was you.
--C'mon!
--[SHIRLEY, RIVALZ] Huh?
[TAMAKI]
Halt! You--!
[LLOYD]
Well, Miss Cecile?
How are the test
parts working out?
They're ready to be
practically applied.
It's back on!
Unlock your fuel hatch.
We'll replace
your energy filler.
Right.
But why did you come out
here, too, Miss Cecile?
[CECILE] Good question.
Why did we, Lloyd?
Why else? To recover
the Lancelot!
And to do a few
other things, as well.
It's a Sutherland arm,
is it showing contact?
[SUZAKU] They've cleared
the compatibility check.
[CECILE] Good. Now leave
this place to us.
You go after Zero!
[SUZAKU gasps]
Thanks to you, I will.
Please protect Ashford
Academy and everyone here!
[LLOYD] Yes. After all,
my fiancée is here, too.
--[beeping]
--[SUZAKU] Hm?
Royal private channel?
[CORNELIA]
K-Kururugi...?
[SUZAKU]
Viceroy Cornelia!
Damn their tenacity! I'd expect
that of Cornelia's elite!
[ZERO]
Tohdoh!
[TOHDOH]
Hm?
[ZERO] From here on,
I'm leaving all operations
in your hands!
Ohgi's been wounded.
Have Diethard assume his duties!
Hold on a second!
What do you mean,
leaving them to me?!
[ZERO] I'm afraid there's
another urgent matter
that requires my attention!
I won't respond to any further
communications from you!
W-Wait!
What else could be more
urgent than this, Zero?!
[COMM 7]
Seventh Squad wiped out!
What?!
[MILLY]
Remain calm!
You're safe, so wait your turn!
Youngest students go first!
[BLACK KNIGHT 1]
We've gotta fall back!
[BLACK KNIGHT 2] Destroy
any records you can't take!
[BLACK KNIGHT 3]
Hurry! Hurry!
[OHGI groans]
[CORNELIA]
This battle situation...
...bodes victory for my forces.
Am I clear?
Do all you can to hide the
fact that I've been wounded.
It'll only upset them...
Guilford...
the Glaston knights...
You're the only one...
...I can tell...
[SUZAKU]
Don't try to talk any more.
Kamine Island... that's
where Zero's headed.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[CORNELIA]
Any more than that...
It's no use... I
can't remember...
Geass!
Y-You're Euphy's
knight, aren't you?
Then you must go and
clear her dishonored name!
[SUZAKU gasps]
Yes!
I know... this is
a bit informal...
But I dub thee Knight
of Honor of Britannia.
You are now a knight in
both name and station.
Go, Suzaku Kururugi!
Yes, Your Highness!
What?! Does this mean
that Zero's disappeared?
[DIETHARD] Not at all, he
simply transferred command
to us on-site here.
--Right.
--[beep]
[DIETHARD]
Why? Why now, of all times?!
[TAMAKI] I wanna know
why Ohgi was shot!
And where the hell is Zero?!
[MINAMI]
I said I don't know!
Can't someone get
a hold of him?!
It makes no sense.
He had no reason to run away.
In spite of Tohdoh's experience,
if he doesn't see
the entire picture...
Zero... I don't know
what to do next.
--[ringing]
--[KALLEN gasps]
[OHGI]
Kallen...
Ohgi! Are you all right?!
Yeah...
Kallen, listen to me...
Go after Zero!
[KALLEN]
Hm?
[OHGI]
There's must be...
...a reason... he's
acting this way...
Save him...
Zero...
The one who will realize...
...Naoto's dream.
[KALLEN]
But-- How do I find him?!
[OHGI]
You should see it soon...
[KALLEN gasps]
That's... the Lancelot!
What would be drawing
him away from here?
Rakshata... put a
transmitter... on it.
[KALLEN]
Understood.
Supply corps!
Send a captured air
transport to me ASAP!
It's top priority!
Dammit!
Can't we at least
hold this place?!
It will only be until all the
students have boarded the ship.
Hang in there.
Yes I will.
[gasps]
Why am I reading a thermal
reaction in there?!
A Knightmare!
What in the world is
that antique doing here?
Ganymede...?
[gasps] Nina!
Oh, hell! Cease fire!
That goes for you,
too, Black Knights!
Huh?
[LLOYD]
Call a temporary truce!
We can't fire on that!
Listen, everyone, do as he says!
Hold your fire!
[RAHSHATA] If it's got Lloyd
that panicked, then...
[LLOYD sighs]
[LLOYD]
Nina, did you complete it?
[NINA] There wasn't
enough time to test it.
I don't know if it'll explode.
Still... I'll try to.
[MILLY] Nina! What did
you mean by "explode"?
[CECILE]
It's dangerous! Stay back!
You see, if her
theory is correct,
that thing may destroy the
entire Tokyo settlement.
[MILLY gasps]
--But that isn't possi--
--[RAKSHATA] Believe it!
[RAKSHATA]
She's even using Sakuradite!
[TAMAKI gasps]
Zero, where is he?
Tell me where he is!
Princess Euphemia
will be avenged!
Where is Zero?!
[LELOUCH]
If I've lost Nunnally,
then what have I been
fighting for till now?
What's the point of this
war of independence?!
Why did Euphy have
to be sacrificed?!
[C.C.]
Kamine Island in sight.
[LELOUCH gasps]
I'm taking Nunnally back!
No matter who tries to stop me!
It figures it would be here.
Do you have some sort of
connection to this place?
Not this one.
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
Meaning there are other
places similar to this one.
Does Nunnally's abductor
have a Geass power?
[C.C.]
I don't know that much.
[LELOUCH grunts]
[C.C.]
It's the truth.
I don't doubt it.
We're still accomplices,
so at the very least,
I should give you the
benefit of believing you.
Thank you.
--[C.C. gasps]
--[LELOUCH] What's the matter?!
I see! This is--
--[gasps]
--[LELOUCH] What?!
[C.C.]
Calm down!
We're caught in a trap
that was set for intruders.
The one who activated it--
[C.C. gasps]
[LELOUCH groans]
[LELOUCH]
What is this?
The past?
C.C.!
No!
But...
[SOLDIER]
Hold it right there?!
[C.C. gasps]
[screams]
[LELOUCH]
Stop it...
Stop it!
C.C., these... visions...
...are these of your...
[C.C.]
All I have left are my memories
from when I was a witch.
Other than that,
I don't even know if I was
ever human to begin with.
Every person who
has ever hated me,
and each and every one that
has shown me any kindness...
are gone... forever.
They've vanished into
the current of time.
Always existing with the
endless flow of eternity...
...I am utterly alone.
You are not alone!
[C.C.]
Huh?!
We're each other's accomplice.
Therefore, if you're
supposed to be a witch,
then perhaps I
should be a demon.
[C.C. chuckles]
Odd thing to say at
a time like this.
C.C., you okay?
Don't you know who
you're talking to?
[C.C. gasps]
[JEREMIAH]
Zero! It is I!
Repent is now!
Stubborn ass!
The section Cornelia
damaged before!
There's one shot left
in the Hadron canon!
It's time for my
wonderful vindication!
[JEREMIAH]
Insidious isolation impudence!
[C.C.]
I'll handle this lunatic!
You go after Nunnally!
[LELOUCH]
But... we're out of energy!
[C.C.]
I'll be all right!
[C.C. sighs]
Well... I am nervous.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
You have to prevail,
over your own past,
and over the outcome
of your own action.
[LELOUCH]
C.C., don't die.
Who are you talking to?
[LELOUCH chuckles]
You have a point.
[JEREMIAH]
I've found him!
You're not my first pick to
commit suicide with, but--
[JEREMIAH screams]
Hold your ground!
Victory's within
our reach! Be strong!
[CHIBA]
Dammit, we can't hold out!
[ASAHINA] Enemy reinforcements
will be here soon!
[SUGIYAMA]
What should we do?!
[INOUE gasps]
Inoue...?
Where the hell is he?!
Zero!
All forces, charge!
We'll smash these filthy
rebels with one blow!
[TOHDOH]
Fight till your last breath!
Stop at nothing!
Because if they
break through here,
our forces will
collapse completely!
[DIETHARD]
It's not that Tohdoh isn't
a brilliant military leader...
He simply lacks the incredible
charisma Zero possesses!
We need him! He can't
run out on us, not now!
[KAGUYA] Oh Zero, have
you really abandoned us?
Have you abandoned Japan?!
[LELOUCH]
That trap at the entrance
was designed to buy them time.
Was I the intended target?
Or was it C.C.?
No matter.
The first thing to do is make
sure Nunnally is all right.
[gunshot]
Turn and face me... very slowly.
[LELOUCH]
Dammit! Why now?!
[SUZAKU]
Didn't you hear me... Zero?
I said turn and face
me... very slowly.
[ZERO]
Euphemia randomly murdered
throngs of innocent
Japanese people.
You'd fight for a woman like--
[SUZAKU] Your Geass power
is quite convenient, isn't it?
[LELOUCH gasps]
[SUZAKU]
You get to hide in the shadows
while others take all the blame
for doing your dirty work.
You're just an arrogant coward.
That's your true nature,
the "real you."
Kallen!
[KALLEN gasps]
[SUZAKU] Don't you want to know
Zero's true identity, too?
[KALLEN]
What are you saying?!
[SUZAKU] You have a
right to bear witness.
[KALLEN gasps]
No, wait!
[KALLEN]
But how...?!
How could you?!
[SUZAKU gasps]
I didn't want it... to be you.
L-Lelouch is...?
[LELOUCH]
Yes.
I am Zero.
The man who leads
the Black Knights,
who challenges the
Holy Britannian Empire,
the one who holds the
entire world in his hand.
[KALLEN whimpers, sobs]
[KALLEN] You used us,
the Japanese people?!
You used me?!
[LELOUCH] And as a result,
Japan will be freed.
You certainly can't
complain about that.
[KALLEN gasps]
I should have arrested you
when I had the chance.
[LELOUCH]
You knew it was me?
I wasn't sure at first.
So I convinced myself
that it wasn't true.
I really wanted
to believe in you.
But you were lying
to us, to me...
...your sister, Euphy...
...and Nunnally!
[LELOUCH]
Yes.
And now, Nunnally's
been kidnapped!
[SUZAKU gasps]
[LELOUCH] Please, Suzaku, can't
we call a temporary truce?!
I need your help!
Together, we'll be able
to save Nunnally!
There's nothing in the world
that you and I
can't do together!
I'm done with that.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Had you only joined
up with Euphy first,
we wouldn't be here!
If you and she had
combined forces,
things would be different!
The world could have--
[LELOUCH]
That's all in the past!
Over and done.
[SUZAKU]
Past?!
[LELOUCH] You killed your
own father, didn't you?!
Wallow in remorse when
you have time for it!
N-No! You're hopeless!
[LELOUCH]
What?
I know you! In the very end,
you'd betray the entire world!
The way that it's betrayed you!
I'm not going to let your sick,
twisted dream be realized!
[LELOUCH]
You fool!
You think ideals alone
can change the world?!
Fine! Then go right ahead
and shoot me! Come on!
Set your aim on this
liquid Sakuradite!
[KALLEN gasps]
[LELOUCH] If my hearts stops,
this vial will explode!
You'll both die with me!
[SUZAKU]
Damn you!
[LELOUCH] Listen, I'll
make a deal with you.
I want to know who
told you about Geass.
Did they abduct Nunnally?!
Nothing that happens now...
is any of your concern!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[SUZAKU] Your very
existence is a mistake!
You need to be erased from
the face of the earth!
I'll take care of Nunnally!
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch!
[gunshot]