[C.C.]
The one time a man never lies
is when he makes a
vow in his own heart.
Lelouch Lamperouge made a vow
to avenge his mother
and to create a world
where his sister Nunnally
could live in happiness.
To that end, he obtained
the power of Geass.
To that end, he became Zero.
And, he undertook
all that followed.
At the very least,
that was the truth as it
seemed to Lelouch at the time.
Big brother,
the promise you made...
[LELOUCH]
Yes. I'll keep it.
[SUZAKU] So you've agreed
to the Special Zone.
That doesn't wash away the
blood that's on your hands.
[GINO]
Suzaku.
I know, Gino, we've gotta
pull back this time.
[OSI AGENT]
The Black Knights seem to be
diving back underwater.
Shall we pursue the Vincent?
[VILLETTA]
Unnecessary.
Suspend the search for C.C.
until we receive further orders.
[VILLETTA sighs]
Be careful, Rolo.
If they get you,
they'll catch me
in the same net!
[ASAHINA] Join the Specially
Administrated Zone?
What is he thinking?
[CHIBA]
Who knows.
Ohgi.
[OHGI]
Huh?
If Zero is making decisions
that aren't in the interests of
the Japanese people, then...
Are you meaning?
[door hisses]
[OHGI]
Hm?
[KALLEN gasps]
Zero, listen.
Master Zero!
How could you leave
your new wife waiting?
[ZERO]
Lady Kaguya,
I'm glad to see you're
well and as lively as ever.
And I see you're still
surprising everyone
like you always do. Offering to
join the Special Zone!
No one expected that at all!
Yeah, she's right.
What was that all about anyway?
I told ya, he's just
bluffing so we can lure
the Britannians
in and nail 'em!
[ZERO] Fighting, then more
fighting and then what?
[ALL]
Huh?
Hold on!
What are you saying,
we should dance with them?!
We fight because we must!
Unless you know some
other way to do this.
No, we can never make
friends with our conquerors.
The Japanese people
are fighting for freedom.
[ZERO]
Tohdoh! What is "Japanese?"
[grunts]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Attention all Elevens.
You can now process your
Special Zone applications.
Ah, what do we do
about the Special Zone?
Please don't loose your nerves
about it at time like this.
[ELEVEN 1] Is this going
to be another massacre?
[ELEVEN 2]
Zero said if we get behind it...
[ELEVEN 3]
We'll be their slaves.
[ELEVEN 4]
Dammit, I just got a work permit
as an honorary Britannian!
[ELEVEN 5]
Exactly.
What's the point of being
"Japanese" again?
[ELEVEN 6] So only people
without jobs should join in?
[FEMALE REPOTTER] Thus far,
no elevens have signed up
for the Specially
Administrated Zone of Japan,
commonly called
the Special Zone.
As there has been
no contact from Zero,
some officials speculate that
he may be facing dissension
within his own organization,
the Black Knights.
[LOHMEYER]
I'd like you to please stick
to the prepared
manuscript this time.
[NUNNALLY]
I was acting as viceroy--
[LOHMEYER]
A viceroy is not a king.
Viceroys act as official
representatives of the emperor,
ruling each area
prudently on his behalf.
We will support your attempt
to revive the Special Zone
this time. But henceforth,
please consult with me on
such matters beforehand.
[RIVALZ]
Leave of absence?
[SUZAKU]
Yeah.
It looks like I'm going
to be a little busy.
With the Special Zone huh?
Oh? And what about all
our plans for the garden?
Sorry, Milly.
I'll be sure to come back
and help out if I get a break.
That reminds me, Suzaku.
Have you thought about Kallen?
[SUZAKU gasps]
[SHIRLEY] Isn't there some
way you can help her out?
[RIVALZ] Yeah, right, like a
plea bargain, you know.
Something like that.
We all know you're working
for world peace and all,
but family and friends
are important too, right?
Couldn't you discuss
it with the Viceroy?
Like when you had me talk to her
on the phone the other night.
Huh?! What?
You talked to her, Lulu?!
[gasps]
With the young princess?!
Uh, well, It was on the
night of the welcome party.
She mistook me for someone else,
so it was kind of a hazy call.
[RIVALZ giggles]
You botched it up.
[ALL laugh]
[SUZAKU] Lelouch, have you
really lost your memory?
Or, are you covering up?
If you do remember,
this is what I'd like to know.
Why did you have
to kill Euphie?
Surely you could have
found another way!
Suzaku Kururugi,
you traitor! Time to die!
[ZERO]
Live!
[ASSASSIN grunts]
[GUARD A]
Sir Kururugi!
[GUARD B]
Are you alrigjt, sir?!
[SUZAKU] You, who used your
Geass to force me to live,
knowing that in my heart,
I sought the
punishment of death.
Someone like you.
[DIETHARD] Yes, that's right
I believe it will be.
We've already sent
Sayoko Shinozaki there.
[ZERO]
I see. Well done, Diethard.
You really are
an expert at this.
An outstanding job.
You're truly irreplaceable.
[gasps]
Thank you for those words!
I'm deeply honored!
Are you sure your plan
for the following stage
will be consistent?
Yes I am. Our tactics
may have changed, but our
strategic objective
remains the same.
Take care of things on your end.
[ROLO] You haven't forgotten
your promise, have you?
[LELOUCH]
No.
I will protect this school.
You and I live here
now as brothers.
I won't let anything
interfere with that.
But, I reject the
Britannians' phony claim
to control our destiny.
[ROLO] I'm helping you because I
have something to protect now.
If you were discovered,
this school would be
destroyed and everything lost.
Right. And then
there's V.V. as well.
Mm-hm. He'd kill me as a
traitor without any hesitation.
And I'd be slain in
the next moment.
So we share the
same destiny, you and I.
[door hisses]
[VILLETTA]
Sorry I'm late.
Club activities ran over-time.
Uh... so, Zero, what can I do?
Please, Ms. Villetta,
just saying that name
could cost us our lives.
Lelouch, what did you want?
[LELOUCH]
About Ohgi. Do you miss him?
[gasps]
[RESEARCHER A] Alphabet Effect
confirmed in fifth. Countdown:
--20, 19, 18...
--[door hisses]
--[KANNON] I'm back, Nina.
[gasps]
[NINA]
Kannon!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hello. It's been a while.
[YOUNG RESEARCHER]
Prince Schneizel as well!
[NINA] When did you
get back from the E.U.?
A short time ago.
I just completed peace
negotiations with the French.
[NINA] In that case, you should
keep pushing forward.
If you press victory
too hard or too fast,
you're inviting defeat.
[gasps]
In every corner of the world,
people look for hope.
Our victories can trample
that hope underfoot.
That can be true of
enemies and allies.
Everyone has something
they yearn for.
[gasps]
What?
[meows]
You're Suzaku's cat, huh?
[footsteps]
[SUZAKU]
He seems to like you, Anya.
[ANYA]
Japanese clothes?
Yes, I always wear them for
any of my training sessions.
Do you miss them?
Japanese things?
Yes, I wonder.
I do have some
good memories, but I--
Sir Kururugi, I've been
looking for you.
[SUZAKU]
What is it?
[CLAUDIO]
I need your signature on this.
It's the order to execute
the Eleven who tried to
assassinate you, sir.
[SUZAKU sighs]
[CLAUDIO]
I need authorization from
a Knight of the Round to
carry out the sentence.
The experiments are continuing.
I won't squander the faith
you've shown in me, your grace.
I promise.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hm?
[gasps]
I haven't forgotten.
During the
Black Rebellion, when...
[gasping]
[gasps]
Why didn't it work?
[yelps]
Cécile!
[CECILE]
Right!
[NINA]
Professor Lloyd, stop!
[MILLY]
Nina!
Milly, you, too?!
Please let me kill Zero now!
Let me avenge Princess Euphemia!
[NINA]
That prototype was a failure.
But if you give me
a little more time,
I'm certain I can
build one that works.
You were thinking of Euphie.
You did all of it for her sake.
History may remember her
as a tragic figure,
but I still believe in my sister
and wish to honor her memory.
So do Cornelia and Nunnally.
Also Kannon and Suzaku and many
others whose lives she touched.
And you. You believe in her.
And that's why I believe in you.
I'm grateful, Your Highness.
Excuse me.
Is something wrong, sir?
[SUZAKU gasps]
I'm a Round, I'll sign it.
Yes, that's fine.
Thank you, ma'am.
Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
Hm?
Are you some
kind of... masochist?
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
You know you're disliked here,
yet you volunteered for Area 11.
Hated as the hero
of the Numbers.
As a traitor to Japan.
As the man who killed Zero.
You're always on trial here,
and out of envy and hatred,
they try to pull you down.
There's no point in
trying to make people
understand why I'm
doing all these things.
Because there was someone
who did understand.
Anyway, when you get
down to it, I am a sinner.
[GINO]
Hey there, you two.
[SUZAKU]
Uh?
Looks like we gonna get that
call we were waiting for.
The one from Zero.
[grunts]
[CECILE gasps] Should I
really be here for this?
[LLOYD] You wanted to
see Zero, didn't you?
[CECILE]
Yes, but...
[SUZAKU] Sorry, all the
other rooms are in use
for Special Zone perparations.
Oh, I see.
You have to keep this
confidential too, I guess.
Is there some diplomatic
reason for that outfit?
Ah! Yes ma'am, I apologize.
Here it comes now.
[CECILE gasps]
[ZERO]
Ah! Three Knights of the Round.
However, I don't see
the Viceroy with you.
We don't need to worry
her with the details.
Excuse me. I just
wanted to ask you,
are you the same Zero as before,
or are you a brand new one?
[ZERO] Zero's truth is
not based on who is within.
It's the actions
that measure the man.
[LLOYD]
Ah-hah! A philosopher!
You said you'd stop fighting
and join in the Special Zone,
but do you have full consensus
on that from all of
the Black Knights?
[ZERO]
I have more than that.
A million people
have been mobilized.
A million?!
And they'll all participate?
[ZERO]
Yes, but there's one condition.
You must let me go.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[ZERO] Of course,
you'll have to explain this
to your own people,
so I suggest you punish me
by sending me into exile.
[SUZAKU]
And the Black Knights?
[GINO]
He doesn't care about them,
he just wants to
save his own skin.
[LLOYD]
If word of this gets out,
your own people
will string you up.
[ZERO] That's why I've
taken the precaution
of keeping these talks secret.
[ANYA]
How boring.
[LOHMEYER] Area law,
section 12, paragraph 8.
It is within the
viceroy's authority
to apprehend subversive
or rebellious elements
and send them into exile.
Miss Lohmeyer!
Are you suggesting
we let Zero go?!
I'm simply stating the
legal basis of action.
[ZERO]
In that case,
you can make the announcement
at the opening ceremonies.
That's some kind of sweet deal?
If the big terrorist runs away,
the little terrorists will
shake and quake and disappear.
Perhaps. But where is justice?
[SUZAKU] Our legal counselors
have confirmed that exiling
Zero would be appropriate
and within precedent.
[NUNNALLY] Right, that might
be for the best.
Crimes have been committed.
My own desire to forgive
them is a personal matter.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
Would you mind
doing this, please?
I wrote Euphie's
name right, didn't I?
[SUZAKU]
Mm-hm.
Euphie, we're going to
make your dream a reality.
A peaceful and
gentle world, for you.
[gasps]
Uh. Is something wrong?
No. It looks like
there's someone else
who's still grieving
for Euphie's death.
I wonder who it is.
I'm glad there are others
who loved her like we did.
So, are you finished now?
[LELOUCH]
Yes, that was the last thing.
There's nothing
holding me here now.
This is the area of
the Shizuoka ghetto
that will soon become
the Special Zone.
A huge number of Elevens has
already gathered for
the opening ceremony.
As there are over a million
people here, verifying personal
I.D.s will have to wait
till after the event.
The presence of
this many Elevens
is a clear testament
to the enormous power
and influence that
Zero still commands.
[GINO]
What they don't know
is that Zero has already
betrayed them all.
[CREW MEMBER A]
You think there'll be a riot?
If there is,
we'll have the perfect excuse
for a full scale crackdown.
Ah, but remember,
We don't move until
they do, got it?
[CREW MEMBER A]
Yes, my lord.
[gasps]
[OHGI]
It can't be. Chigusa?
[VILLETTA] Kaname Ohgi are
you out there somewhere?
Thank you for coming and
for taking me back home.
Are you alright with this now?
Of course, I was
just an acting consul.
Once a new consul is chosen I
simply have to return home.
Besides, this is an
excellent opportunity.
But, what about
the Black Knights?
The request I made
to Britannia yesterday
should set us up for the future.
[coughing]
Lord Xing-ke,
are you all right?!
Don't be concerned.
I just have to last
a little longer.
[NUNNALLY]
People of Japan,
Welcome to the Specially
Administrated Zone.
I'm overjoyed that
so many of you
have gathered here
for this great event.
Please, lend me your help so
we can make history together.
[CLAUDIO] Lord Guilford,
you're in no condition for this.
The Japan Special Zone was
Princess Euphemia's dream.
[DAVID huffs] But there's still
no sign of Zero anywhere.
That's because the
man is a coward.
He'll only show up when he
thinks we can't get to him.
[LOHMEYER] Now then, before the
ceremony officially begins,
there is a matter we wish
to confirm regarding Zero.
As imperial subjects,
all those participating in
the Japan Special Zone
will have criminal charges
against them reduced.
And criminals that are
class 3 or lower
will have their
sentences suspended.
However, the instigator
of the murder of former
Viceroy Calares
cannot be forgiven.
Therefore, under special Area
law, section 12, paragraph 8,
Zero alone shall be
banished and sent into exile!
Huh?!
Only Zero?
So that means he gets to
run away all by himself?
[ZERO] Thank you,
my Britannian friends!
[NUNNALLY gasps]
[ZERO] I am grateful for
your lenient treatment.
So he came here after all.
[GUILFORD] Make your move, Zero.
If there's a riot,
we have full license to wipe
out all the radical elements.
Duly authorized
by Miss Lohmeyer.
Show yourself, Zero!
I'll escort you safely out
of the country myself,
I guarantee it!
[ZERO] I don't wish to be in
your debt, Suzaku Kururugi.
However, I have a question.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[ZERO] What does it mean
to be Japanese? A nation.
What?
[ZERO] Is it language?
Territory? Blood lines?
No! That's not it!
It's in the heart!
[ZERO]
Then we're in agreement.
A feeling within.
Of belonging. Dignity. Pride.
The culture is
carried in the heart.
You're Japanese no
matter where you are.
[gasps]
[SUZAKU] And what
does that have to do
with you running
away by yourself?
[TOHDOH]
Zero.
[gasps]
[LOHMEYER]
I figured they'd try something.
What is it? What's going on?
Viceroy...
[GUILFORD]
So be it.
All forces, prepare to
cut them down!
[PILOT A]
Yes, my lord.
Hold on!
They haven't made
any violent moves yet!
[GINO] Zero may be the
one who planned this,
but does he have the guts
to come out in the
open and show himself.
[LOHMEYER]
Well, well.
It looks like he was right here
on the grounds all this time.
[gasps]
--[SUZAKU gasps]
--[LOHMEYER] All of them!
[NEWS REPORTER]
This is outrageous!
Zero has appeared,
but not as expected!
That is--
So this was your plan!
Despite our
overwhelming firepower,
you've figured a way to
move a million people.
[ZERO] Viceroy Nunnally has
ordered Zero into exile.
Since we are all Zero, we must
all leave this country at once.
What?!
[ZERO]
No matter where we go,
we are Japan, for we
carry it in our hearts!
[gasps]
[ZERO]
Let us set out for a new land!
[KAGUYA]
Come on, all you Zeros!
Let's go to a new world!
[TAMAKI]
Time to get exiled, everybody!
We're all Zero,
so we're all outa here!
[ELEVEN A]
That's right! I'm Zero!
[ELEVEN B]
Let's get deported!
[ELEVEN C]
I'm Zero too! Come on!
Ah-hah!
He wanted a legal excuse to
get them all out of Japan!
We prepared for a riot,
but we might have
to let them go.
Don't panic, it's a bluff!
There's no way he can
transport a million people!
[MESSENGER] We just got
word from the port authority.
The port? They wouldn't!
The Chinese Federation
requested safe passage for...?
[MESSENGER]
Yes, the iceberg Ship.
But the applicant has
already left the country.
It can't.
[ELEVEN A]
We're getting on that?
[ELEVEN B]
But, it's ice!
[ELEVEN C]
Won't it melt?
[RAKSHATA]
We'll be fine!
The iceberg ship
is indestructible.
It has so much insulating
polymer and super-Berthier film,
the ice will never melt.
[DAVID]
Target the leader!
Take out the real Zero!
[PILOT B]
Right! But...
[PILOT C] How do we
know which one is him?
[RIVALZ]
This is...!
[SHIRLEY]
What's gonna happen?
[MILLY] It's that Zero's more
than an idol now, he's a symbol.
[sighs] He's made himself into
a living avatar for everyone.
[VILLETTA]
Elevens! Take your masks off!
[TAMAKI]
Britannian witch!
[OHGI]
Don't shoot!
Don't let them drag
us into a fight;
that's not why we're here!
Ohgi, is that you?
[OHGI]
Uh, no. I'm Zero.
[NUNNALLY]
Please tell me what's going on.
Miss Lohmeyer has stayed behind
for operational oversight.
You mean leave
everything to her?
It'll be all right.
[NUNNALLY gasps]
Suzaku is there with her.
Sir Kururugi,
we can't let a million
laborers leave the country!
Make an example of--!
Hold on, please!
Zero!
Order them to take
off their masks!
Do it now or there'll
be another massacre!
[TOHDOH] Only if you
order it, Suzaku!
And even if we're all unmasked,
no one would know
who the real Zero is.
Sir Kururugi!
This is an act of rebellion!
Order us to fight!
[OHGI]
He's wrong.
This is a way of resolving
things without fighting.
[GINO]
It's your call, Suzaku.
You're in charge.
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Zero we could let you escape,
but a million people?
To let them all go with you?
[LELOUCH]
If the Black Knights leave,
peace will come to Area 11.
And Nunnally's reign will
no longer be threatened
by our presence.
[SUZAKU] Even so, this is
a dirty way to do it!
[LELOUCH] Give the order!
To let Zero go!
[SUZAKU] I must give
the order to shoot Zero!
To kill him!
[LOHMEYER]
Hm.
I'll do it! Zero!
[gasps]
[NUNNALLY]
Crimes have been committed.
My own desire to forgive
them is a personal matter.
[gasps]
That's right!
[LOHMEYER grunts]
Euphie and Nunnally both
wanted to forgive him!
We're dealing with Zero!
Zero's to be exiled!
That was our agreement.
If we break it, the people
will never trust us again!
The people?! These are Elevens!
Only you speak of them as people
because you are one of them!
This has nothing
to do with that!
If they're all subversives,
why do you want them here?!
So you can massacre them?!
They've challenged
Britannian rule,
so let them burn in hell!
Shouldn't we get rid of these
disruptive elements then?
They're exiling themselves!
[LOHMEYER]
But...!
[SUZAKU]
Zero, can you promise
that you'll lead
them to salvation?
[ZERO] Of course.
And you, Suzaku Kururugi,
can you promise the
ones who stay behind
will find salvation
in your hands?
That's exactly why I became
a Britannian soldier!
[ZERO]
I understand.
I will trust in the
promise you've made.
[ZERO]
Did you hear that? All Zeros!
Sir Kururugi has declared it!
Rebels are hereby exiled!
Nothing holds us back now!
Forward! To the land of freedom!
[ELEVENS chatter]
[TAMAKI] Let's go while
we have the chance.
[OHGI] Goodbye then,
Lady of Britannia.
[growls] A perfect
chance to kill them all,
and he's throwing it away!
My lord, Xing-ke.
[XING-KE]
Hm?
It sems the Area 11
operation has succeeded.
I see.
Looks like Zero's
next performance
will be... on our stage.
[LLOYD] So, Suzaku managed
to save a million lives,
and no one will ever
thank him for it, eh?
I think he knew that going in.
He's used to it now.
[SUZAKU] His whole plan
was based on one prediction:
that I would give the order
to hold fire and let them go.
You know me well, Zero.
[LELOUCH]
You are my worst enemy.
I know you Suzaku.
And I also know Nunnally.
I know her heart.
That is why I could
foresee the outcome.
And, for now,
I am grateful to you,
Suzaku Kururugi.
Don't ever forget the
promise you've made to me!
No matter how I multiply
the avatar of Zero,
There is still only one Zero.
That's right, Zero is...
I am... the one
who killed Euphie.
Which makes me a terrorist.
And so, Nunnally,
even your pure heart cannot
forgive my crimes. I have to
call forth a miracle to atone
for the sins I've committed.
That's why, Suzaku. Why I've
turned towards tomorrow.
Your becoming a Knight of
the Round changes nothing!
I do this to battle
your power as well!