[C.C.] In this world, evil can
arise from the best intentions.
And there is good, which can
come from evil intentions.
How then should Lelouch's
actions be taken?
Every man has his day of
judgment, does he not?
[C.C.]
Geass...
He who uses this inhuman power
will find his heart isolated,
whether he wants
it that way or not.
Thus, he plummets into the abyss
that lies between good and evil.
But if a man can climb out
of that abyss into the light,
then that man has
the soul of a king.
Yes, that's right. The training
for the post-refit Guren MK-II
is proceeding on schedule.
Kyoto and the Military
District of India
have finally come to terms.
So, we're just waiting for
Rakshata and her team to arrive.
And the organization's
changeover to a
cell-based structure
is now 92% complete.
The members have also
been ranked into 14 tiers.
As you directed,
we've infiltrated
all Britannian warehouses.
Within the Kanto block,
combat personnel have been
dispersed to 564
separate locations.
Thirty-two of our positions
have been uncovered.
Eleven of those were dummies.
Fourty-seven members
have been apprehended...
But since information
is now fire-walled
above class 8 members,
the Britannians aren't
getting anything out of them.
And now that we have
the unreserved support
of the Kyoto Group, we're
seeing almost no more cases
of citizens tipping
off the authorities.
On that list of
Britannian supporters...
Yes, it's the group you
made arrangements with.
Oh! And we're still
looking for information
about Tohdoh and
the Four Holy Swords.
--[PA] A176 to the Chinese
--Understood.
--Federation is now
--Continue with the work,
--boarding.
--all right?
Are you sure you want
me to be the messenger?
If you look humble
they'll look down on you.
That's how it works in
the Chinese Federation.
I don't know about that,
but unlike you, I do
have some humility.
Good, now you can put it to use.
How's your passport?
[C.C.]
Not a bad forgery.
I'm all set.
[NUNNALLY]
Where we going?
Are we getting moved to
another place again?
It's one of the
Kururugi's homes.
This time it's the
main house, okay?
Keep on walking, Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
But...
[LELOUCH]
Keep walking!
Where are we?
It smells really bad here.
We're going by a garbage
dump, right, Suzaku?
[NUNNALLY]
What's wrong, Suzaku?
[SUZAKU]
I... I...
[sobs]
Nunnally...
My mother taught me that a
warm touch is good for tears.
Do you think it's true?
[LELOUCH]
I will overcome this.
[bell chimes]
[SUZAKU panting]
Hey! Lelouch!
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
What's up?
You know, they're
going to hold you back
if you don't start
coming to class.
I could say the same
about you, right?
I have work to do.
It's just that the Black Knights
have really been
on the move lately.
Hey, I thought you
were in engineering.
[SUZAKU]
Uh...
We're shorthanded so
they move me around.
[LELOUCH]
Hm.
Still, how about dropping
by for dinner more often?
Nunnally misses you.
Are you free this evening?
Yeah, I could come tonight,
but are you sure it's okay?
--I don't wanna cause any-- Ah!
--[tires screech]
[RIVALZ]
Hey! Lelouch!
What's wrong?
[RIVALZ]
I heard the President's out
doing a blind date thing again!
Yeah. Today.
Today?! Why didn't
you tell me about it?!
Because it'd make you cry.
Boys don't cry!
It's okay; I didn't
know about it either.
Don't give me your emo routine!
Emo?
I guess compassion is
not in fashion these days.
So anyways, are we on for
dinner tonight with Nunnaly?
[SUZAKU]
Sure!
What about school?!
Don't worry, I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna go
tell her about it!
[RIVALZ] My life is over and
he's worried about dinner.
--[NUNNALLY giggles]
--[door opens]
--[NUNNALLY] Uh?
--[footsteps]
My classes don't start
till second period, Sayoko.
--[NUNNALLY] Huh?
--[clapping]
[clapping continues]
[MAO]
Heh.
Are you surprised?
[MILLY]
Uh...
[LLOYD]
Matchmaking dates are usually
in hotels or restaurants.
[MILLY laughs nervously]
I suppose that's true.
But I'd heard you were a very
unique person, Lord Asplund.
[LLOYD]
Unique!
What a delightfully
artful way to put it!
[MILLY] I'm surprised
you're interested in a girl
from the downgraded Ashford
family after it lost its rank.
Oh-ho! But I couldn't care
less about loss of rank.
[CECILE]
Excuse me.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Not at all, take your time.
[LLOYD]
No need for that.
Why draw it out?
Let's get married.
[MILLY]
Huh? That's it?!
Getting cold feet?
Nunnally! Suzaku's gonna--
[footsteps]
[LELOUCH growls]
[phone rings]
[LELOUCH gasps]
[ringing continues]
[LELOUCH]
Yes?
[NUNNALLY]
Lelouch!
Nunnally! Where are
you right now?!
[NUNNALLY] I don't know...
But I can't move!
[LELOUCH]
Nunnally!
[MAO]
It's me, Lulu!
[LELOUCH gasps]
It can't be!
[MAO]
You dropped your guard, Lelouch.
Just 'cause you
thought I was dead?
[LELOUCH]
Mao, listen!
C.C. isn't here right now!
[MAO]
That's why I came.
Someone immune to my Geass
would be troublesome now.
I'll save my encounter
with her for a later date.
First, I'm going to pay you back
for that little
session the other day.
[LELOUCH] You're somewhere
within 500 meters of me.
[MAO]
Of course.
Want to try and find me?
[LELOUCH growls]
[MAO]
Your time limit is 5 hours.
Oh, by the way, since the game
is just between you and me,
no using the cops
as pawns this time.
I don't really want
to get shot up again.
Although Britannian
medical science is amazing.
You can thank them
for my return!
[laughs]
You know, Lulu, when you used
your Geass on those cops,
you should have told them to
kill me, not just shoot me.
You left off the
finishing touch,
and now your
sister's in a "bind."
What a quandry! What a
quagmire! What a crunch!
[LELOUCH] Nunnally has
nothing to do with this!
[NUNNALLY] It's not a very nice
way to play a game, you know.
[MAO]
Hmm?
[NUNNALLY] If you do something
to make my brother sad,
I'll never forgive you!
[MAO laughs]
What a pair you are!
I love this brother
sister thing!
[chiming]
[GIRL A]
Hi, everyone!
It's lunch time! Are
you all eating well?
A fight? Shirley and Lelouch?
Right, she's pretending
she doesn't know him,
and the President said
we're supposed to play along
Oh... Right! What's up
with her blind date?!
Never mind that, if Shirley
and Lelouch are fighting--
Leave 'em alone. It's just a
little lovers' spat, that's all.
[SUZAKU]
Uh... But you...
Don't even think that way;
I've got nothing to do with him.
[RIVALZ] So, he hasn't
taken the plunge yet, huh?
The plunge?
[RIVALZ] Well, Lelouch
is good with theories,
but he's not so good
with the real thing.
Real thing?
[RIVALZ] I mean, he
doesn't have "experience."
Experience?!
--[SUZAKU] Ah!
--[BOTH] Huh?
--[SUZAKU groaning]
--[ARTHUR growling]
What's the matter?
Don't you like your food?
Arthur, why do you
always do this?!
[LELOUCH panting]
Hey, Lelouch, what happened
with you and Shirley, huh?
[LELOUCH]
Huh? What?
[RIVALZ]
Just give her some flowers.
And what about your classes?
You'd better go to-- Uh...
[LELOUCH]
Excuse me.
Oh, and I'll talk to
you later about dinner.
You think he's going
gambling again, huh, Arthur?
Huh?
[phone beeps]
[MAO] Lulu, if you do a
handstand while searching
for me, I'll extend your
time limit an hour!
[LELOUCH grunts]
He anticipated this!
He wants to see me squirm.
But what do I do?
He must be within 500 meters
if he's readin' my mind, but...
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[SUZAKU]
That's...!
[LELOUCH gasps]
I thought so... Something's
happened to Nunnally!
[locks clicking]
[VILETTA]
Welcome back!
[OHGI]
Uh... R-Right.
Good timing!
The meal's almost ready.
[OHGI]
Meal?
You mean-- Did you go
out shopping somewhere?
[chuckles] No, I just
used what you had around.
Some people here are afraid
of Britannians, so...
Have you been able to
remember anything yet?
Sorry, nothing at all yet.
[OHGI]
That's okay.
Don't push it.
You're still healing.
It's all right if it
takes time to remember.
--[dishes clink]
--[VILETTA] Okay, it's ready.
I sure hope you like it.
Uh...
[SUZAKU]
Who kidnapped Nunnally?
It can't be a Brittanian or
someone from the royal family.
[LELOUCH] No, this has nothing
to do with our bloodline.
Just a psychopath who wants
to keep a girl all to himself.
[SUZAKU]
So, he's threatening you?
[LELOUCH]
Yes.
An investigation could
reveal who we are.
That's why I can't go to
the army or the police.
[SUZAKU]
Then there's no choice.
We'll have to do it on our own.
This isn't about your
gambling though--
[LELOUCH] It has
nothing to do with that!
[SUZAKU]
Okay.
Do you have any leads?
[LELOUCH]
Just this photo,
and I know that he's somewhere
very close by, watching me.
[gasps]
And now that I think of it,
I heard the sound of
running water, too!
Water...
The circulation system!
[LELOUCH]
The lower levels!
[SUZAKU]
Something's still off though.
[LELOUCH]
What?
[SUZAKU] Normally, you'd
hone right in on that.
[LELOUCH growls]
[SUZAKU]
What is it?
[LELOUCH]
He changed the codes.
We'll have to hack
into the system.
[SUZAKU]
But that's against school rules.
[LELOUCH]
I'll change it back later.
[SUZAKU]
Then let me do it.
[LELOUCH]
Too late; I got it.
[SUZAKU]
That was fast.
You're a little
too good at that.
[LELOUCH]
The student council
has partial access
to these areas.
Lelouch, I see, this
is how you've been
getting off campus, isn't it?
Your little escape route.
Huh?
Uh, yeah... Sometimes.
How's it look?
You were right,
the door's guarded.
There's a machine gun linked
to the security camera.
The lag on these systems is
tight: point zero five seconds.
That means we can't
access it this way.
We'll have to head back up
and disable the main--
[gasps] Wait!
[LELOUCH]
Of all the reckless moves!
Come on, let's go!
Nunnally's waiting for us!
[MAO chuckles]
[LELOUCH, SUZAKU]
Nunnally!
[NUNNALLY gasps]
Lelouch and Suzaku, is that you?
[LELOUCH]
I'm so sorry!
--I'll cut you loose--
--[SUZAKU] Wait! Wait!
Up there!
A bomb.
[MAO]
That's right, Lulu!
I'll play along since
Kururugi came on his own.
Can't wait to see how
you two deal with this!
[LELOUCH grunts]
[SUZAKU] Nunnally, we're
going to diffuse the bomb.
It's okay, don't worry.
Lelouch and I can do anything
together, you know that?
[NUNNALLY gasps]
That's right!
[MAO laughs]
[LELOUCH]
It's motion sensitive.
A solenoid inside
supplies energy
that keeps it constantly moving.
If an external force
interferes with the motion,
then the bomb...
[SUZAKU]
...explodes.
Moving Nunnally even
an inch will trigger it.
That's the way it's set up.
[LELOUCH]
Can you calculate its range?
[SUZAKU]
It'd wipe out everything
within five or six
hundred meters, minimum.
[LELOUCH]
Now what?
We're beyond the
reach of his Geass.
Is he trying to mislead me?
Do you know how to disarm it?
Theoretically.
The power line to the detonator
would need to be severed.
Since he's not a pro at this,
I'm sure I could figure out
which lines are dummies.
Still, we need to find
another way to do it.
[SUZAKU]
Why?
I-If we choose the right one--
Because you'd have
to cut the line
without disrupting the
motion... which is impossible.
I'll do it; there's no choice.
No, Suzaku! We don't have enough
information to pull it off!
There's a time limit here!
We can't afford to play it safe!
As for information, it's
staring you right in the face...
I'm a soldier, Lelouch, can
you use that information?
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
[SAYOKO humming]
We still have toilet tissue...
[phone rings]
[SAYOKO]
Hm?
[ringing continues]
Huh?
[overlapping voices]
[MAO]
Stuck up little brats!
No wonder I hate school so much.
Huh?
[LELOUCH]
What now?
What's he got
planned for me next?
That camera trained on
Nunnally's transmitting to Mao.
Is he here?
I can't believe he'd still
be here at the school.
What a whack-job.
I told Suzaku to
stay with Nunnally,
but that leaves me
with only one option.
Well, if it isn't Cassanova!
[MAO] No weapons, no strategy,
you didn't diffuse the bomb,
didn't deploy the Black
Knights, or your friend.
What's wrong, Lulu?
I'm not explaining
anything to you.
The final game,
is it ready?
[MAO]
Hm. Let's put an end to this...
...with your specialty.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[CORNELIA]
It's been a while
since we could
spend time like this.
There've been so many unexpected
events since we came here.
[EUPHEMIA giggles]
All of that desk work--
it's making you fat.
Hey, cut it out.
That's not funny!
[BOTH laugh]
Cornelia, don't you think
this garden looks familiar?
It's like Lady Marianne's.
Now that you mention it...
[EUPHEMIA]
I heard Clovis ordered
them to build it like this.
[CORNELIA] I'm surprised he
liked her villa that much.
Since he was always fighting
with her son, Lelouch, there.
He must have thought
of Lelouch as his rival.
[CORNELIA] Even though
Lelouch was younger?
[EUPHEMIA] Well, he kept
paintings of Lelouch
and the others; we found
them after he was killed.
[CORNELIA]
I see...
We need to stabilize this
area and capture Zero, fast.
To avenge Clovis... as well
as Lelouch and Nunnally.
This land has taken the lives
of three of our siblings.
It's soaked in our
family's blood.
[MAO] You see, the scale
is the bomb's detonator
and it's cancellation switch.
The chess pieces we
capture will go here.
If the needle swings
all the way towards me,
the bomb goes off.
If it swings towards you,
the bomb will be disarmed.
In short, if you win the game,
your sister's life
will be saved.
Your mind is twisted;
no wonder C.C. left you.
[MAO]
Provoking me won't work.
I can read your thoughts, so I
know what you're trying to do.
[MAO] I'm afraid you're
not the type of person
who can keep your mind empty.
[MAO] There's a part
of you that's a critic,
constantly watching
your own moves,
and then there's another part
that's an observer, watching
the critic watching you.
You're that kind of person.
[chuckles] But I know
all your thoughts,
so I'm always a step ahead.
You can't win.
[LELOUCH grunts]
Bravo!
Your plan is to think
of seven things at once
to confuse me and trip me up.
But you see, if I focus
my Geass directly on you,
it's easy to tell which
one is your true thought.
[LELOUCH grunts]
[MAO] Aah, your last
plan is failing as well.
You underestimated me;
that's why your sister is...
[LELOUCH gasping]
"What do I do?"
"I'm out of strategies.
I can't call for back up
as long as Nunnally's
being held hostage!"
[LELOUCH gasps]
[MAO]
Sorry, sorry, I dropped it.
[LELOUCH sighs]
[grunts]
[MAO]
Your turn.
Better hurry.
Lookie, lookie,
time is running out.
Your little sister's
not going to make it.
Ah, is that the right move?
Are you sure you
want to do that?
[LELOUCH gasps, sighs]
Isn't this enough?
[MAO]
Huh?
Please stop it, Mao.
[MAO]
I can't hear you very well.
You got everything you wanted!
Let Nunnally go!
Huh?
I admit it...
You have beaten me.
[MAO laughs]
Very well said!
You're finally
speaking the thoughts
from the deepest part
of your soul, huh?
That feels great! Fantastic!
[MAO]
But no.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[MAO] ]
This is...
[LELOUCH gasps]
Checkmate!
[LELOUCH yells]
No!
[LELOUCH gasps]
Nunnally...
[MAO] Hm... Let me se if
she's burst into little pieces.
Huh?
[gasps]
What? Why is she...?
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[MAO gasps]
How did you--?!
You kept me focused on you!
[MAO groans]
[grunts]
I am Warrant Officer
Suzaku Kururagi
of the Britannian military,
and you are under arrest!
Suzaku.
You disarmed the bomb?!
Impossible! You'd have to match
your speed to the pendulum!
[SUZAKU]
That's right.
After Lelouch showed
me which line to cut.
[LELOUCH]
I showed you?
What are you saying?
It was your plan.
Cut the line, then bust in
here when I heard you scream.
My plan?
[gasps]
So that's it.
Right...
Mao, it seems that
it's my checkmate.
[MAO] Lelouch, don't
tell me that you--
[LELOUCH]
Yes...
I gave Suzaku his instructions,
then used Geass on myself
to forget, so you
couldn't find out.
You believed that if you
know a person's thoughts,
you know everything.
That's why you
narrowed your range
and focused all your
power on my mind.
That was your mistake.
That's ridiculous!
You bet everything
on one friend?!
What if he'd failed you?!
[LELOUCH]
Good point.
To execute this plan, I had
to trust Suzaku completely.
Sayoko, everything's fine now.
Right, go ahead.
Sayoko?
I'll have you free in a second.
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
You think you beat me, huh?!
[SUZAKU]
Stop it!
Get your hands off
of me, father killer!
[SUZAKU gasps]
[LELOUCH gasps]
[MAO] You killed your own
father seven years ago!
Hmph!
He called for
do-or-die resistance,
and you thought stopping
him would end the war.
What a childish idea!
The fact is, you're a murderer.
[SUZAKU]
That's not true! I just-- I--
[MAO] How lucky for you
that no one ever found out.
All the adults lied
to protect you.
But all the reports
said his suicide
was a protest against
the military actions--
[MAO]
A big, fat lie, all of it.
A lie?
I didn't have any choice!
If I didn't, Japan would have--
[MAO] That's how you
justify it in retrospect?
Well, it explains
your deathwish!
[SUZAKU gasps]
You want to save people's lives?
It's your own wretched soul,
you're trying to save!
That's why you're always
charging into danger!
Placing yourself on
the edge of death!
[SUZAKU gasps]
[screams]
[MAO]
You're no hero.
You're just trying to wash
the blood off your hands.
A little brat begging
to be punished!
[LELOUCH]
Mao!
[MAO gasps]
Never speak again!
[MAO]
Huh? No!
[MAO choking]
Mao!
I did love you, Mao.
[MAO choking]
Mao, I want you to go and
wait for me... in C's world.
--[gunshot]
--[MAO groans]
I just... I just...
[LELOUCH]
I'm a fool.
In the end, I never
asked the terms
of the contract
she made with Mao.
And Suzaku...
When we were reunited,
why didn't I-- No!
He's been trying to tell
me for a long time now.
I should have confronted
him right from the start.