[BOTH]
Huh?
[NARRATOR]
The date was August 10
in the year 2010 of
the Imperial calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire had
just declared war upon Japan.
The far east island nation had
held fast to its neutrality,
and now Britannia looms as
the world's only superpower.
Rights to Japan's
underground resources
became a hotly disputed issue,
straining the already
deep-rooted diplomatic tensions
between the two sides.
In the deciding battle
for the mainland,
Britannian forces
introduced into combat
the humanoid autonomous
armored knight
known as the Knightmare Frame.
The enemies forces were far
greater than anticipated,
and the Knightmares obliterated
the Japanese line of defense
on the mainland
with little effort.
Japan became a
dominion of the empire.
The country was stripped
of its freedom, its rights,
and its name.
Area 11.
The defeated and
once-proud nation of Japan
was re-christened
with a mere number.
[LELOUCH]
I swear...
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[LELOUCH]
I swear, Suzaku, so help me!
I will one day...
obliterate Britannia!
[COP 1]
This is Alpha 3.
Target is traveling from
Delta-12 toward Delta-14
at a speed of 80
kilometers per hour.
[COP 2]
CCP to all mobile units.
Declaring a code 3
from floor 5 to floor 2.
All units, take 2-8-8.
I want the target intact.
Here's video footage
of yesterday's
terrorist bombings in Osaka.
The Secretary reported 59
casualties in this incident.
Eight Britannians and 51 others.
[gasps]
[MAN]
You're out of time.
From here on, you'll make
your moves every 20 seconds.
Huh! Very well, I'm game.
[gasps]
[NOBLEMAN]
Hm?
Did your substitute arrive?
[OWNER]
Thank heavan, I'm saved.
Are things going well at school?
What have we here?
School boys?
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
Well, look at this, a nobleman.
I envy you kids today, you have
so much time on your hands.
Time for regrets...
What's your name?
Lelouch. Lamperouge.
Whoa, now wait a minute!
You can't win this one,
it's impossible. Right?
Rivalz.
[RIVALZ]
Huh?
When do you think
we would have to leave
in order to make our next class?
Uh, 20 minutes,
if we bust our hump.
Then be sure that you drive
safely on the way back.
Huh?!
[LELOUCH]
I'll need nine minutes.
And by the way,
about yesterday...
[OWNER] Understood, sir.
We'll discuss it later.
[NOBLEMAN]
Nine minutes?
You only have 20
seconds per move.
Enough time.
[NOBLEMAN]
Hm?
You start with the king?
[laughing]
[MILLY]
Where's Lelouch?
[SHIRLEY]
He went somewhere with Rivalz.
[MILLY] What, maybe
it's poker this time?
[SHIRLEY]
They seem to forget
that they're on
the student council!
They're off gambling for money!
Lulu may be smart,
yet he wastes his brain
on stupid things!
If he'd only apply himself in
school, he'd get high grades!
"Oh, I wish my darling Lulu
would be a serious young man."
How adorable is that?!
Uh. Please, Madam President...
Perfect!
After we finally steal
this damn thing!
It's all because Tamaki
couldn't stick to Naota's plan!
And now we've got a problem!
[RIVALZ] I love playing
against the nobility!
When they lose, they
always pay out of pride.
By the way, eight minutes,
32 seconds is a new record!
[LELOUCH] He also didn't have
much time to move, either.
And as opponents go,
the nobles are tepid.
They're just over-privileged
parasites, that's all.
[RIVALZ] Well then,
why don't you challenge
one of the Elevens? They're
nothing like us Britannians.
Huh?
[MAN]
What're they trying to prove
by killing innocent people?
[WOMAN]
Those Elevens terrify me.
[NEWSCASTER]
We apologize for the delay.
Now, His Royal Highness
Prince Clovis,
third prince of Britannia,
will address the nation.
To all my imperial subjects!
Including, of course,
the many cooperative Elevens
who choose to serve
the empire of Britannia!
We're not "Elevens,"
we're Japanese!
[CLOVIS]
Do you not see my pain?
My heart was ripped from my
chest only to be torn apart!
The remnants are filled
with rage and sadness!
However, as ruler of Area 11,
I will not tolerate
terrorism of any kind!
Because the battle we
fight is a righteous one!
A virtuous battle to protect
the well-being of one and all!
Now then, everyone,
I would like you to join me in
observance of the eight who died
for justice in the line of duty.
[NEWSCASTER]
A moment of silence, please.
Well, aren't you gonna join in?
[LELOUCH]
Aren't you?
[RIVALZ]
Heh! It's sort of embarrassing.
And I agree with you.
Besides, spilling tears
over those people
won't bring them back
to life, now will it?
Dang! That's dark, buddy!
[LELOUCH] It's all about
self-satisfaction.
Doesn't matter how hard you try.
You can't do it.
There's no way you
can change the world.
[LADY A] You were magnificent,
Your Highness!
One would never guess
that you were attending
a party while doing that!
After all, the viceroy is
the marquee actor of Area 11.
I need to change
costumes quickly.
[LADY A]
My! You're so self-confident!
It's all in the performance.
Since the media want
a charismatic prince,
I give them one.
Untrue! Prince Clovis,
our key purpose in life
is to support and assist
your reign in any way we can!
His reign is a pathetic sham.
[BARTLEY]
Y-Your Highness!
Huh? A soldier?
Gad, how boorish of you.
[BARTLEY] I beg your pardon,
Your Highness, m'lord--
Not another appearance for him.
Hope it's not as dreary.
[BARTLEY]
You fool!
[DIETHARD]
Hm?
The police were informed
that it's medical equipment,
that's all.
If we scramble the army,
there'll be a record--
Deploy the royal guard!
The Knightmares as well!
[CONTROLLER]
Alert 1! Alert 1!
Fourth, seventh. and eighth
rapid reaction companies
as well as the 31st air assault
team, immediate scramble!
Special division nine,
stand by for deployment!
[RIVALZ]
That first move you made.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[RIVALZ]
Why'd you start with the king?
If the king doesn't lead,
how can he expect his
subordinates to follow?
What's with that?
With what?
[RIVALZ] Do you fantasize about
running a major corporation?
[LELOUCH]
No way.
Ambitions like that
will ruin your health.
Uh.
[RIVALZ]
Waaaagggh! We're gonna die!
You idiot! Watch
where you're going!
[KALLEN]
No, not that way!
[RIVALZ]
Eh... Was that our fault?
[LELOUCH]
I don't think so.
Uh?
[COP 1]
Control, the target has crashed
at the abandoned V.O.
building construction site.
[HQ] The military will take over
General Bartley's command.
[COP 1]
Him?!
[BARTLEY] We have to
retrieve it at all costs!
That thing...
in the wrong hands...
What the--?
Oh, man, this sucks!
Looks like the power line
on the bike got cut.
Yeah... Rivalz,
come check this out.
[MAN 1]
Hey! Over here!
[MAN 2]
Whoa... nasty crash.
[WOMAN 1] What happened,
some sort of accident?
[MAN 3]
Probably a drunk driver.
[WOMAN 2]
It's always some moron!
[MAN 4] Hey, maybe
somebody oughta go help.
[LELOUCH]
Hmph. All those idiots...
[RIVALZ]
Wait!
[BYSTANDERS chattering]
Look, the student rescue
team has arrived!
So like, why doesn't somebody
call for help, y'know?
[LELOUCH]
Hey! Are you all right?
[RIVALZ] Yeah, yeah, I know
it's the right thing to do,
but I wish the guy would
quit flaunting his pride
and just give it
a rest for a while.
Now we're gonna
be late to school.
[KALLEN]
Nagata! Nagata!
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?!
[FEMALE VOICE] It's you...
Finally, I have found my--
But where--?
[LELOUCH]
Are you in there?
Stop! I'm in here!
[RIVALZ] So, would you
call that a hit-and-run?
You'd think they'd stick
a ladder on the inside, too!
--[SOLDIER A] Stop the vehicle!
--[LELOUCH gasps]
[SOLDIER A] Surrender now,
and you'll get the chance
to defend yourself in court.
Stop and surrender at once!
[SOLDIER A] Give up now,
or we will shoot to kill!
Now whadda we do?!
That's the Army!
[KALLEN] Have you forgotten?
That's what I'm here for!
[LELOUCH]
If I jump out, I have the choice
of breaking my neck
or getting shot.
I can try to call-- Uh.
[KALLEN] Can you enter the
subway via the Azabu route?
[NAGATA] Kallen!
Let's use it here! Why not?!
Because that would
mean a blood bath!
[NAGATA]
You're right...
[LELOUCH]
I've seen her before...
Lelouch, c'mon, where are you?
We've gotta get to school!
[SOLDIER A] Target is moving
from the settlement
toward the ghetto.
[SOLDIER B]
Copy that! Corner 'em!
[SOLDIER A]
Roger!
[SOLDIER C]
A slash harken?!
A Knightmare!
[LELOUCH]
Crap!
These guys are real terrorists!
You fellas know full well what
this bad-ass mother can do!
[JEREMIAH]
The rest of you, back off.
I'll take this guy.
[JEREMIAH] I can only assume
you dug that obsolete relic
out of some scrap heap.
An over-the-hill Glasgow
is no match for a Sutherland!
Not to mention a filthy Eleven
who spurns the compassion
of our glorious emperor!
[NAGATA]
Kallen, we should both split up!
Both of us can't risk
being killed! Run for it!
[KALLEN]
But--!
[gasps]
Heh. Simple-minded Eleven.
No way! It's stuck!
[JEREMIAH]
Secondhand junk!
I'll admit, I really
like your spirit.
However...
[LELOUCH]
Tsk! No cell phone reception...
We're out of range.
Judging from the darkness
and road surface,
we must be drivin' along
the old subway lines.
They're headed for an exit
somewhere in the ghetto.
Getting out will be dangerous.
Still... Okay, I've got it...
I'm not big on the military,
but I'll take their protection.
If I give them a
terrorist communicator...
Oh, wait, I forgot...
Some friend! Leaving
me behind like that!
Ah-ha!
What're you doing?
Looking at a man who
blundered, am I right?
Why you...!
[LLOYD]
You really screwed this one up.
Terrorists came along
and stole whatever it was
that you and Prince Clovis
were secretly working on.
Retrieving it is simple,
but you want to sweep up all of
their compatriots, in addition.
Let the terrorists go, and
you can find their hideout, too.
Congratulations! Your
reasoning was on spot on!
Uh, it was nothing.
I just thought it was strange.
[BARTLEY]
Okay, that's enough!
What is it the special
corp wants outta this?
I'm merely saying that I'd like
to assist with the clean up.
[BARTLEY]
To assist?
Correct, because
it's data I want.
Excuse me,
but what in the world have
they just stolen, anyway?
[BARTLEY]
Chemical weapons.
In other words... poison gas.
[CAPTAIN] The terrorists are
hiding in the subway system.
Your mission is to locate
the weapon that they've stolen.
Investigate the old subway
system that runs through
the Eleven residential district
in the Shinjuku ghetto.
Report in the moment
you spot them.
Recovery of the target will be
handled by us, the royal guard.
You people bear the honorary
title of Britannians now,
but you were born Elevens.
Therefore, the stench
of these monkeys
oughta be a familiar one.
If you want to earn
the right to carry arms,
then show some results!
This is your opportunity to
show your loyalty to Britannia!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, my lord!
An accident? Or else--
No... the tire's stuck...
[NAGATA]
Please, Ohgi... Find me...
[SQUADDIE A]
4-0-4 has sighted the target.
[CAPTAIN]
Roger! Prepare for recovery!
[LELOUCH] Now I can use
this chance to climb up.
Are you Britannian?
That's enough mindless murder!
Wait! I'm not one of--!
[SOLDIER]
Planning to use poison gas?
[LELOUCH]
Huh?!
[SOLDIER]
Don't play dumb with me!
Get off me!
I'm not here by choice!
And if that's poison gas, it was
made in Britannia, wasn't it?
[gasps]
My god...
Mindless murder?
Then why don't you just
obliterate Britannia!
[SOLDIER]
Lelouch...
It's me. Suzaku.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
You...
You became a Britannian soldier?
[SUZAKU]
Yeah, and what about you?
You're a--
[LELOUCH]
What're you saying?!
That's not poison gas...
What is it?
[KALLEN] In all the confusion,
I left it in the coat.
[OHGI]
It's okay.
The Glasgow's
circuits are usable.
So, were we right?
Think so.
I bet it's poison gas,
like intelligence said.
[OHGI]
And Nagata?
[KALLEN] I dunno. I think
he made it underground.
[LELOUCH]
Tell me the truth, Suzaku.
Poison gas? This girl?
Hey, it's what they told us
in the briefing, I swear!
Huh?!
[CAPTAIN]
Stinking monkey.
Being an honorary Britannian
will not excuse you!
[SUZAKU] Uh! But sir! I was
told this was poison gas!
How dare you question orders!
[LELOUCH]
This is bad.
A poisonous situation.
Which would pose a threat
to Suzaku's superiors
if it's unleashed.
However, in light of
your outstanding
military achievements,
I'm going to be lenient.
Private Kururugi, take this
and execute the terrorist.
--[SUZAKU grunts]
--[LELOUCH gasps]
[SUZAKU]
But he's not a terrorist!
He's a civilian who got
caught up in all this!
[CAPTAIN]
You insubordinate little--!
That's an order!
Didn't you swear your loyalty
and your life to Britannia?!
[SUZAKU]
Yes, but...
But... I can't.
[LELOUCH]
Uh.
[CAPTAIN]
What?
[SUZAKU]
I won't do it, sir.
I won't shoot a civilian.
I can't follow your orders, sir.
[CAPTAIN]
Very well.
[gunshot]
Suzaku!
Well, Britannian school boy,
not a good day to cut class.
Collect the girl.
After you've secured her,
kill the student!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, my lord.
[NAGATA]
Death to...
...Britannia...
[NAGATA]
Long live...
...Japan.
[BARTLEY]
They got away?!
And you call yourselves
the Royal Guard?!
[CAPTAIN]
Uh. Forgive me, my lord!
The blast was mainly directed
upwards, but the bed--
[BARTLEY]
Why the hell do you think
I only told you
people about this?!
[CAPTAIN] W-We'll continue
the investigation.
[CLOVIS] The plan has moved
forward to the next phase.
B-But, Your Highness!
[CLOVIS] If knowledge of her
gets out, I'll be disinherited.
Tell them back home
we're carrying out
a planned "urban renewal" here.
As Clovis, third prince of
the empire, I command you!
Destroy Shinjuku ghetto!
Leave no one alive!
[SHINJUKU RESIDENTS screaming]
[OLD MAN]
W-Why are they doing this?!
Dear, let's go!
[OLD MAN]
H-Hurry!
--[door opens]
--[gunfire]
[SOLDIER 1] Okay, let's
sweep the next floor.
[BARTLEY] The enemy is garbage
that can never hope to become
even honorary Britannians!
Wipe out every last one of them!
Naturally.
[SOLDIER 2]
Supervisor Jeremiah,
General Bartley requests
that you take command--
Bartley has staff officers.
I haven't had this much fun
on the front lines in ages!
[CLOVIS]
Hmph.
[LELOUCH]
What the hell are you?!
This chaos is all
your fault, isn't it?!
Aaaggh!
Not only that
but Britannia has...
They even killed Suzaku!
[LLOYD]
Not there?
[CECILE] It looks like
he's gone to the front line.
[LLOYD] Even though we
brought the Lancelot here?
Now what'll do we do?
We steam rolled our way in here,
but we don't have
a devisor to use it.
[LELOUCH]
Stay quiet, and wait here.
[CAPTAIN]
Report.
[SOLDIER C] We found
only Elevens here, sir.
[CAPTAIN]
Ahhh.
You're sure of it?
That exit comes out here?
[SOLDIER C] Yes, sir. It matches
up with our map of the old city.
[BABY crying]
[gunshots]
[phone ringing]
[CAPTAIN]
Hm?
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
That jerk! He hung up
on me! I can't believe it!
[CAPTAIN]
What an appropriate location
for a terrorist to meet his end.
[LELOUCH]
You scum...
[CAPTAIN] Still, you did
well for a student,
but that's to be expected.
You're a Britannian.
Unfortunately, my
clever young friend...
...you have no future.
He mustn't die!
[LELOUCH]
You shot her!
[CAPTAIN]
Hmph.
Our orders were to bring
her back alive, if possible.
Oh well, nothing can
be done about it now.
We'll tell our superiors
that the royal guard
found the terrorist hideout
and killed them all.
Regrettably, the female hostage
had already been
tortured to death.
What do ya think, school boy?
[LELOUCH]
How can this be happening?
First Suzaku's killed...
then this girl...
Now I'm about to die...
...before I've had a chance to
do a single thing with my life.
It's gone in a heartbeat...
Nanally!
[gasps]
[FEMALE VOICE] You don't
want it to end here. Do you?
[LELOUCH]
What?
[FEMALE VOICE] You appear
to have a reason for living.
[LELOUCH]
The girl? That's impossible.
[FEMALE VOICE] If I grant
you power, could you go on?
I propose a deal.
In exchange for this power,
you must agree to make
my one wish come true.
Accept this contract, and
you accept its conditions.
While living in
the world of humans,
you will live unlike any other.
A different providence...
A different time...
A different life.
The power of the king
will condemn you
to a life of solitude.
Are you prepared for this?
[EMPEROR] A convergence with
the Ragnarok Connection?
So the myth is
beginning once again?
[LELOUCH]
Yes!
I hereby accept the
terms of your contract!
[CAPTAIN]
Hm?
[LELOUCH]
Say, how should a Britannian
who detests his own
country live his life?
Are you some kind of radical?
Huh?
[LELOUCH] What's wrong?
Why not shoot?
Your opponent is
just a school boy.
Or have you finally realized?
The only ones who should kill
are those who are
prepared to be killed!
[CAPTAIN]
Uh...
What's happening here?
I, Lelouch vi Britannia,
command you!
Now, all of you...
...die!
[CAPTAIN chuckling]
Happily, Your Highness!
[CAPTAIN]
Fire!
[LELOUCH]
That was the turning point.
Since that day,
I've lived a lie.
The lie of living.
My name, too, was a lie.
My personal history, a lie.
Nothing but lies.
I was sick to death of a world
that couldn't be changed.
But even in my lies, I refused
to give up in despair.
But now this incredible
power... it's mine.
Well, then!