We hereby declare
the resurrection of Japan
as a lawful independent
and sovereign nation!
Atsushi Sawasaki,
leader of the forces
that have occupied
the Fukuoka military base,
was Chief Cabinet Minister
of the Kururugi Administration
in the former nation of Japan.
After the war, he fled
to the Chinese Federation,
but is apparently
making his move now
in response to the recent
civil unrest caused by Zero.
Whether the Black Knights
have played a role
in these unfolding events
is still under investigation.
[TAMAKI]
We're not part of it!
[OHGI]
What does Kyoto say about it?
They didn't know
this was coming.
They were just notified
about his unilateral claims
over the Sakuradite
mining rights.
Zero, it's our move.
What are we gonna do?
[NEWSCASTER] Sawasaki's group
was working in conjunction
with a terrorist
organization in Kyushu.
After cutting off vehicle
access from Honshu and Shikoku,
and with support from
Chinese Federation forces
from the Liaodong
Military District,
they are expanding
their occupation
around Fukuoka,
Nagasaki, and Oita.
According to General Tsao,
the Chinese Federation is
providing humanitarian support,
and is not...
[LLOYD]
So how's Suzaku doing?
He says that he'll do
whatever the mission demands.
[LLOYD]
I see.
And what about
Prince Schneizel?
Where is he?
In the Tokyo Settlement.
Got there after
his run-in with Suzaku.
Avalon doesn't have
its commander right now,
but we have to finish this up
if we want to counter
the Gefjun Disturber.
[SUZAKU]
I've dishonored you.
I'm not worthy
to be your knight.
If this is about
your disobeying orders,
my brother Schneizel said
it was an unusual situation,
and you shouldn't
be blamed for it.
[SUZAKU]
I can't forgive myself.
Please...
Has knighthood become
a burden for you?
Something that troubles you?
[SUZAKU]
No, I'm grateful for it.
Then why?
[SUZAKU]
I've remembered something.
I... I killed my own father.
I was never punished for it.
I just lived on
like nothing happened.
And right now I'm
being protected again!
While soldiers die and
Elevens suffer, I'm unscathed.
A person like me
doesn't deserve this!
You don't deserve it?
Then I don't either.
[GUILFORD] Princess Cornelia,
we're taking too many losses!
This tempest is preventing us
from using our air power!
We'll have to delay
the landing operation
until the weather changes.
[CORNELIA growls]
It's a stroke of good
fortune that this storm hit.
We must use it to
tighten our grip on Kyushu.
You see, Gen. Tsao?
Heaven is on our side.
We're going to prevail
in this battle with ease.
[SCHNEIZEL] Martial law
is not necessary.
Such measures would only
upset and frighten people.
Contact E.U. Foreign
Minister Gandolphi.
Oh, and put a call in to
the Toromo Agency in Cambodia.
Prince Schneizel,
using the Toromo agency
could be a--
Prime Minister!
Yes, Euphy. Something wrong?
[EUPHEMIA] Is there
anything I can do to help?
I'm the sub-viceroy of Area 11,
I should be assisting you.
Thank you.
Just your offer to help me
is more than enough.
But I...
[DARLTON] The viceroy
gave strict orders
that you not be entangled
in this matter, Princess.
[EUPHEMIA]
She did?
Just because I chose my
knight without her consent...
Oh, uh no,
that's not correct.
I think even the
Kururugi matter--
Please understand, Euphy.
Cornelia can't
take any chances now;
the situation
is too treacherous.
[EUPHEMIA]
You mean...
[SCHNEIZEL] Darlton, concerning
the matter we were discussing,
I know someone who
has a way in with them.
So, I will ask for help.
[DARLTON]
Yes, Your Highness.
[SHIRLEY] After all our
hard work getting ready,
it looks like they're going
to cancel the school festival.
[RIVALZ] That's hardly
a huge consideration
since we're at war.
[NINA]
Did you say war?
They're using this
government in exile
as a smokescreen,
but this is a war with
the Chinese Federation!
[NINA]
Oh, I see...
Nina, what about the booths
we were planning to borrow
from the art museum?
Uh, I'm going there today.
If I have some extra time,
I'd also like to drop
into the science department.
[MILLY] Are you talking
about that present of yours?
Huh? What present is that?
Professor Asplund
said that I should ask him
if there was something
special that I wanted.
You mean Lloyd?!
That philandering playboy?!
That's enough!
Could you get
a little work done?
Easy for you to say;
this is work for three people!
Suzaku's in the army,
Kallen's in the hospital,
and that other fool's
nowhere to be found.
There's something's really
weird about Lelouch lately.
[SHIRLEY]
I was so shocked.
I'm still confused about it.
How can Lelouch be Zero?!
"I still haven't told anyone.
I want to meet you
first and ask you face to face."
[SHIRLEY]
Did I really write that letter?
How is it possible?
Why did I forget that Nunna's
big brother is Zero?
[TECH A]
Z-01, float attachment, contact.
Control line, established.
[CECILE]
That's really amazing.
You got a perfect rating
on the float simulator.
[SUZAKU]
Thank you.
Tell me, why did you want to
give up being a knight, Suzaku?
Well, because...
Princess Euphemia still
approves of me even as I am now.
So if I caused her
any trouble,
if I brought her
dishonor or shame,
I had a feeling that she
would end up hating herself.
[EUPHEMIA]
A figurehead.
That's all I was from
the start; I knew that.
But I thought if
I gave my best effort,
maybe I could make
some difference.
Forgive me, Clovis.
I met Zero face to face,
but I didn't avenge your death.
I have to think of some way
to save Lelouch and Nunnally,
but how?
I don't have the kind
of power that my sister has;
I'm not like her or Schneizel.
No matter where I go,
I'm just a burden
and I act selfishly
though I don't mean to.
I chose my knight against
my sister's advice.
And now he's resigned.
[GUARD] Oh yeah,
they told me about you.
You need to have the documents
signed today, right?
But a member of the royal family
is viewing the art right now.
Huh? Which member is it?
[TAMAKI]
Uh, so you're saying...?
[ZERO] We aren't going
to collaborate with Sawasaki.
He's not independent.
He's a puppet of
the Chinese Federation.
[URABE] But he says
he's fighting for Japan!
[ZERO] We'd get a
new name and a new master,
but nothing would change.
His Japan is a sham.
Yeah, so what you're
really saying is...?
When Britannia strikes back,
we play dead?
[DIETHARD] Zero, perhaps
you'd better clarify
what our overall mission is.
Yeah, he's right.
Even leaving aside
the Sawasaki matter,
what's our mid-term
goal on this?
[ZERO] To make Tokyo
an independent nation!
Independent?!
A nation?!
[KNIGHT A]
Are you serious?!
[KNIGHT B]
You mean us?
[KNIGHT C]
A country?
[KNIGHTS muttering]
I thought so.
He's really going all the way!
Wait a minute!
No matter how much the
Black Knights have expanded...
Our enemy is an empire
that controls
one third of the world!
We can't pull that off alone!
[ZERO]
Then answer this!
Are you just going to sit back
and wait for someone else
to defeat Britannia?
Who?
You think if you
wait long enough,
someday the right chance
will finally come?
Don't be naïve!
If we don't stand up
and do it ourselves,
that "someday"
will never come!
[NINA]
Princess Euphemia!
[GUARD]
Secure the perimeter!
Code Delta!
We have a Code Delta!
[NINA]
Please!
I just want to thank
Princess Euphemia!
To get one look at her!
[GUARD] Repeat, lock down all
gates leading into the building!
[EUPHEMIA]
From the hotel!
[GUARD]
We've caught a suspicious girl
at the building perimeter!
Watch for any
unidentified vehicles!
Stop it!
That girl is a
personal friend of mine!
[NINA gasps]
[CORNELIA]
Good. It's cleared up.
[GUILFORD] Now we can resume
the landing operation.
And we'll try to put Prince
Schneizel's plan into action.
You think the Special Corps
can break through their line?
[GUILFORD]
With Kururugi, it's possible.
[CORNELIA] Using him
can also mean trouble.
[GUILFORD] But there's no
commander on the Avalon now.
Earl Asplund isn't capable.
[RADIO]
Incoming missiles!
Launch point appears
to be Fukuoka base!
One minute,
five seconds to impact!
Not bad!
They're well prepared
against air raids as well.
Are we sending up
a barrage?
[CECILE] We'll be fine
in this position.
[RADIO]
Direct hit confirmed!
The Avalon is destroyed.
Hmph! Even if it is
state-of-the-art,
a single ship
can't possibly hurt us!
Hm? What the...?!
Lancelot's shield
was already proven
on the battlefield.
Major Kururugi,
I'm laying out the mission plan
for final verification.
This ship will breach
the enemy's front line
from high altitude and move
directly to the launch point.
The advanced weapon
system Z-01 Lancelot,
using the float unit,
will attack the enemy
headquarters at Fukuoka base.
The float unit
consumes energy fast,
so pay attention
to your operation time!
[SUZAKU]
Yes, my lord.
M.E. boost...
Lancelot unit, now launching!
[SUZAKU]
...launch!
[RADIO] The enemy ship seems
to have launched a bomber,
but it's moving faster
than a fighter plane!
[RADIO]
I have picture!
[ALL exclaiming]
[SAWASAKI]
A Knightmare!
[TSAO]
It's not being transported,
it's just flying on its own!
That weapons report we got...
could this be it?
You mean that novelty weapon?!
[SAWASAKI]
But then, the pilot is...
[LLOYD] The military force
that's trying to occupy
the Kyushu block
is fighting under
ex-minister Atsushi Sawasaki.
If they lose him,
the new Japanese government
will collapse very quickly.
In that case,
the Chinese Federation
will lose their excuse for being
here, and have to withdraw.
[SUZAKU] There it is.
The enemy headquarters.
[SUZAKU]
An open channel?
[SAWASAKI]
This is Minister Sawasaki.
Is that Prime Minister
Kururugi's son
in the pilot seat?
[SAWASAKI] I see. I didn't know
he had a son like you.
[NINA] And then when you
saved me, Princess Euphemia,
I'll never forget it...
You looked like
some kind of goddess,
like you were bathed
in radiant light.
Oh! Forgive me!
I should have thanked you
for these change
of clothes you gave me!
Oh, don't worry
about that, Nina.
Besides, I'm not all
the wonderful person
you think I am.
I'm no good compared
to my brother and sister...
No, that's not true!
How can you say that
about yourself?
There's not one
good thing about me.
Really, nothing at all.
My parents are ordinary,
I'm not the least bit pretty,
and there's just
nothing special about me...
[EUPHEMIA]
That's wrong, Nina.
I think you're a very cute girl.
[NINA gasps]
Oh, no, I'm not really
good for anything.
Not at all.
[EUPHEMIA]
She hates herself.
But, so do I...
[NINA] I guess I understand,
but Suzaku makes me uneasy...
[EUPHEMIA] That's it.
Suzaku feels badly too!
So please, oh please,
don't say that you're no good,
Princess Euphemia, I beg of you!
Because...
Because I need you.
I need your goodness.
Thank you so much, Nina.
I'm glad I got to know you.
[NINA gasps]
You've really
helped me understand!
[SUZAKU] This has nothing
to do with my father.
I came here to put
an end to this fighting.
I will accept
your surrender.
[SAWASAKI] You want to rob
Japan of its dream of freedom?
[SUZAKU] Freedom has to come
the right way, not like this.
[SAWASAKI]
You'll act out of selfishness?
It's justice without ideology.
No, you're wrong!
That's not what I--
[grunts]
My V.A.R.I.S!
[SUZAKU] Those are Chinese
Federation Gang Lous.
[chuckles] He allowed me
to distract him.
He still has much to learn!
Euphy?
Schneizel!
May I have access to a
private communication line?
My energy filler!
Are you kidding?!
They blasted off the float?!
[CECILE] The Avalon
has to strike at the base!
No, the shield doesn't
completely surround us!
One direct hit and we'll
go down in flames!
Suzaku!
Reroute all power to
combat and com-systems!
[SUZAKU]
Got it!
You had better
surrender, Suzaku.
Since you're Prime
Minister Kururugi's son,
I guarantee that you'll
be very well treated, my boy.
I decline.
If I used my father's name for
this, I'd never forgive myself.
This is between you and me.
[SAWASAKI] I see. You're very
much your father's son,
as foolish and
stubborn as he was!
[EUPHEMIA]
Suzaku Kururugi!
[SUZAKU]
Princess Euphemia!
Suzaku!
The truth is,
you and I uh, that is...
[SUZAKU]
Sorry, but right now...
[EUPHEMIA]
You see...
I hereby command you
to love me!
Right!
[CECILE]
Huh?
What?! What is it?!
Uh, sorry,
but this is private.
[EUPHEMIA] And in return,
I will love you!
Forever!
Princess Euphemia...
Suzaku, I love your
stubborness and your kindness
and your strength.
Your sad eyes, your clumsiness,
and the way you
have trouble with cats.
I love everything about you!
So please,
don't hate yourself!
[SUZAKU gasps]
I see that I've made
you even more worried
than I did before.
You really are--
Everything you do is impulsive!
When we first met,
when you told me
you were a princess,
when you selected my school,
when you made me
a knight... Always!
Yes, they were all sudden.
That's because
I suddenly realized...
But then it's that
spur of the moment feeling
that's opened
so many doors for me.
Thank you!
What are you doing?!
Stop him now!
[SUZAKU] Princess,
can I make one final request?
[EUPHEMIA]
Final?
[SUZAKU] If something happens
to me, whatever it is,
please don't blame yourself.
Destroy all the records
and erase every trace
so no one knows
what happened to me.
[SUZAKU] I don't want
my friends to be sad.
Just tell them I transferred
schools or make up some story.
[EUPHEMIA]
Suzaku, don't tell me you're...!
[SUZAKU] Yes, the Knightmare's
out of energy.
Oh, and please, say goodbye
to Miss Cecile and Lloyd
and to Prince Schneizel for me.
[SUZAKU] I was stubborn
all the way to the end.
Don't die, Suzaku!
You've got to live!
[SUZAKU]
Wh-What the...?
And fire!
--Huh?!
--[RADIO] What was that?!
[RADIO] Something just
appeared on the radar!
A stealth system!
[RADIO]
We've got picture!
[SUZAKU]
That's...!
I see. So the famous white
Knightmare is named Lancelot.
And he's fighting
as recklessly as ever.
[LELOUCH] Yes, but
this time he seems to be
following someone else's plan.
They sent a single fighter in to
try to disrupt the main force.
Even if he fails,
Cornelia can move right in.
[LELOUCH] Schneizel...
Is he behind this idea?
These people are in my way!
I thought the hadron cannon
was still in development.
They made the beams converge?!
But I wanted to be the
one to perfect that system!
[RAKSHATA] Hmm, looks like
integrating the Gefjun Disturber
has worked.
But that float system
is more advanced than mine.
So my opponent
is the Earl of Pudding,
I guess.
We were collaborating
inadvertently.
Oh, how distasteful.
[ZERO] Kururugi, is the
Lancelot still operational?
[SUZAKU]
Zero. I thought so.
It's Zero?
Is that an open channel?!
[RADIO]
Yes!
Then stay with that source
and find out what he's after!
An energy filler?
[ZERO] I'm going to take out
the enemy command center.
What will you do?
[SAWASAKI]
What?!
[SUZAKU] Sorry Zero, but you're
not going to get your wish.
I'm going to hit
them first... my way.
Resume attack!
Stop them!
Stop Kururugi and Zero!
[SAWASAKI]
Zero!
Shouldn't we be fighting
together as comrades?
Don't you care about Japan?
The Black Knights
stand against anyone
who uses violence unjustly
for their own selfish ends!
[SAWASAKI]
Selfish?!
I'm doing this for Japan!
Sawasaki!
If this is for Japan,
why did you run away
to the Chinese Federation?!
[SUZAKU] You should have stayed,
for everyone's sake!
You're still a child!
[RAKSHATA]
A joint operation... Gawain!
[LLOYD]
Lancelot.
So Suzaku and Lelouch are...!
[CORNELIA]
What?! Zero?!
[GUILFORD]
Yes, he saved Kururugi.
Fighting on our side?
What the hell is he thinking?!
[DIETHARD] So his tactic was
to bring the Gawain in alone
to get past the Britannians.
That was brilliant.
Maybe, but the Guren MK-II
could have acted
as a shield for them.
It's not like I can go home
or back to school at this point.
After all our battles,
to be working with
the Lancelot is just...
[DIETHARD] What's necessary
here is not victory.
The Black Knights'
participation in this battle
is an undeniable truth.
Of course, it will never
be officially reported,
but the rumors will spread
and everyone will know
what happened here.
As Zero said,
this will show the world
exactly where we stand.
Protecting the nation
is our first commitment.
[SAWASAKI] What's wrong with
going to another country,
then waiting for the
right moment to strike?
That's an effective
strategy, isn't it?
We can set up a new
line of defense at Kagoshima.
Right. I appreciate your help.
Huh? Huh?!
[SUZAKU]
Sawasaki!
[ZERO]
That's far enough.
[SAWASAKI]
I-Impossible!
They took the largest
fortress in all of Kyushu
with hardly any effort!
The terrorism
in the Kyushu block
led by an anti-government
group was stopped
by Princess Cornelia's
sudden attack.
Atsushi Sawasaki
and four members
of the former Japanese
government were arrested.
Over half the Chinese Federation
troops were captured as well.
In response to this incident,
Chinese Federation
leaders are asserting
this was an unauthorized
action by General Tsao
of the Liaodong District,
and they are requesting
all POWs be released
in accordance
with the Tibet Convention.
Warrant Officer Kururugi,
reporting for duty.
Welcome back home, Suzaku.
--[SUZAKU] Uh... I...
--[EUPHEMIA] I...
[giggles]
[laughs]
Suzaku, I finally
understand my heart.
It's not that I
expect an ideal country
or perfect justice or anything
complicated like that.
I just want to see
people smiling, that's all.
The smiles of
the people I love now
and the people I loved
before as well.
Will you help me?
Will you be my knight?
I will, Your Highness.
[LELOUCH] Now that
Sawasaki's been stopped,
we have to make
our next move quickly!
Also I need to build a place
where Nunnally can be happy.
And for that,
I need to create a nation
that can drive a wedge
into the world.
Things are proceeding
well towards destruction.
And when the time comes,
I'll deal with Cornelia and
Schneizel at the same time!