[GIRL A] Madam President!
Is she all right?
[GIRL B] I don't get this
Chinese Federation thing!
[NEWS ANCHOR] We've just
received an update...
She said that she's sorry, but
she can't buy us any souvenirs.
She's joking about it?
[SHIRLEY]
Thank goodness.
[LELOUCH]
We should make an announcement
so everyone knows she's okay.
[SHIRLEY sighs]
Uh?
Thank you, Lulu.
You're welcome, Shirley.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
Lelouch, got a minute?
[PA chimes]
[PA GIRL]
Attention, all students.
This is an emergency update!
We have confirmation that Milly,
our student council
president, is all right!
She's apparently escaped from
the scene of the coup d'état
in the Chinese Federation
under the protection
of Knight of Seven,
Sir Suzaku Kururug.
[ROLO]
Aren't you getting
a little carried away
with all this?
Oh, does it seem that way
to you? I'm very sorry, Rolo.
[ROLO] You're acting way
too nice to everyone.
[SAYOKO]
But I'm supposed to keep
his relationships
harmonious.
Those were Zero's
exact orders.
Yes, and of course you're
to follow his orders...
But you're not to exceed
your role as a stand-in.
Remember, he's very
self-absorbed.
Yes, I see your point.
After all...
I'm a woman who serves
both Lelouch and Zero.
[VILLETTA] Sayoko, Zero
is in danger right now.
[gasps]
[SAYOKO]
He's in a stalemate
with the Chinese
Federation, right?
[VILLETTA]
Yes,
and Prince Schneizel
just joined the battle.
[ROLO] Uh! Britannian
forces inside of China?!
[VILLETTA]
That's right.
The Knights of the Round
have entered the battle zone.
[TAMAKI] Our reinforcements
aren't coming! What the--?
[OHGI]
Calm down, Tamaki!
We still have the Chinese
Empress as a captive!
They can't just
start shooting at us!
--[explosion]
--[ALL gasping]
[DIETHARD]
What is it?!
[ZERO]
Full scale bombardment.
But that means--
[ZERO] Yes. The Chinese
Federation intends to obliterate
the Mausoleum of Eighty Eight
Emperors and us along with it!
As for the Empress,
they want her to die.
[XING-KE]
The High eunuchs.
They'd violate this
sacred Masoleum
for their petty ambitions?!
All forces, cease fire!
Her Imperial Empress is inside!
[ZHAO HAO] You still don't
understand, do you, Xing-ke?
Generation upon generation
of emperors are buried there.
[XIA WANG]
In short, it's a grave.
A good place to bury
our current empress.
We've already arranged for a
new empress to replace her.
A puppet bride who would
nicely match Prince Odysseus
on their wedding photo.
[XING-KE gasps]
You dare to say this?!
You're the one?
The guy who started
the coup de etat.
[XING-KE]
Stand aside, Britannian!
This concerns my country alone!
[GINO] But, those guys
represent your country,
internationally speaking.
[XING-KE growls]
[GINO]
Besides...
You captured the Guren,
isn't that right?
I happen to have a bit
of unfinished business
with that Knightmare
and its pilot.
[TOHDOH] Remember,
our air power's limited!
Ride with honor,
and strike like steel.
[BOTH]
Roger!
[C.C.]
I'll go out in the Akatsuki.
[ZERO]
C.C.
[C.C. gasps]
[LELOUCH] In case we lose,
have an escape route.
If you come up with a smart
trick, I won't need one.
Second enemy air raid
squadron, coming in fast!
[MINASE] We're not gonna
hold out long against this!
[TOHDOH] Stand aside!
I am Kyoshiro Tohdoh!
What do you know?
They actually brought in someone
good aside from that Guren girl.
[SUZAKU]
Gino. Leave him to me!
[TOHDOH grunts]
Suzaku!
We really could go
down this time.
They've got the Lancelot and
those next generation units...
The Mordred is here!
They're all closing in on us!
All rebel forces,
annihilate them.
Split into three groups!
Surround her and fire!
[ANYA]
Your shells... Useless...
[XING-KE] If I can get
inside her shields...!
Oh, no! I'm leading
the dance at this party!
[XING-KE]
What?!
[XING-KE grunts]
[EMPRESS whimpers]
A single shot from the Mordred's
Stark Hadron cannon
would demolish the
mausoleum, wouldn't it?
[LLOYD] Well, yes, if you
just want to crush them.
[KANON]
And the moment we did that,
they'd say we killed
their empress.
We have to let the High Eunuchs
make that last, mortal blow.
Ah.
So you admit you're outmatched?
Well, we won't accept your
surrender. It's too late now!
[ZERO]
You insist on fighting?
Even though your own empress
will die in the attack!
[ZHAO HAO]
The empress is merely a system.
[XIA WANG] There are plenty
of others to replace her.
So you can't use her
as a bargaining chip.
[ZERO]
But you used her
to gain noble titles in
the Britannian court.
[ZHAO HAO laughs]
You have sharp ears, don't you?
[XIA WANG]
A cheap price to pay for power.
[ZERO]
Cheap? A phony treaty
that gives China's land
to a foreign nation?
[ZHAO HAO] Land is nothing
but dirt, after all.
[XIA WANG]
Correct.
We're Britannian noblemen
now, that's what counts.
[LELOUCH] And what
about the common people
you've sworn to protect?!
[ZHAO HAO] Zero, when you
walk down the street,
do you worry about
stepping on the ants?
[CHENG ZHONG] You throw away
the paper that clings to your
bottom, don't you?
It's the same thing!
[ZERO] You sell out your
country, abandon your empress,
betray your own people,
and all for what?!
[ZHAO HAO]
Ha, an idealist!
I never thought you
were so naive, Zero.
[XIA WANG] Indeed, masters and
commoners will always breed.
[CHENG ZHONG]
Like insects.
[ZHAO HAO, XIA WANG laugh]
Radiant shield generators
two and five are off-line!
That leaves the deck exposed!
[FUTABA]
Ah!
Stop it!
[KAGUYA]
Your Majesty!
[ZERO]
Noblemen? You're bureaucrats,
paper-pushers who know nothing
about noblesse oblige!
Please, stop it. You have
to stop all this fighting!
[GUARD A]
You can't go out there now!
I have to! Out of my way!
I have to go after the Empress!
[gasps]
[XING-KE]
Your Majesty!
What?! My wing!
You let yourself get distracted.
This is wrong!
All of it! All of it!
Do it now.
Fire on the Empress!
[CHINESE SOLDIERS]
We hear and obey!
[XING-KE growls]
[XING-KE] Hang on, Shen Hu!
My life is yours.
Take it if you must,
but save the Empress!
[EMPRESS yelps]
[XING-KE grunts]
Run away, Your Majesty! Go, now!
[EMPRESS gasps]
Xing-ke?
[XING-KE] You finally made
it outside of the city,
but you haven't seen
any of the world yet!
I will defend you here!
But, without you it's
no good, Xing-ke.
It has to be you and I
together! It has to be!
[XING-KE]
Uh?
Your words are wasted on me,
Your Majesty. However...
[ZHAO HAO]
Intensify the attack!
Don't stop till you've
crushed the Shen Hu!
[HONG]
Scum! It can't end like this!
[XING-KE]
I can't save you, after all.
Can't protect you.
For six years,
everything I've done has been
to fulfill my promise to you.
Someone do it!
I don't care who!
But, please, someone save her!
[ZERO]
Very well. I understand.
Wish is granted.
[XING-KE grunts]
Uh! What is that Knightmare?!
It's not only protecting the
Empress, but Xing-ke as well!
[LELOUCH] I ask this of
the Chinese Federation
and the Britannians.
If you want to keep fighting,
are you prepared for
the consequences?
[SUZAKU] Zero? He's come
to the front line himself?
Zero?
But why would he...?
Why are you stopping?!
All units, wipe them out!
So be it!
I gave you your chance,
let no one forget that!
Lloyd, you know what that is!
Yes. We may have lost this one.
Using the Gawain's Druid System
to generate that shield?
I can't believe it.
What kind of scientist
worked it out?
[RAKSHATA]
Knightmare Frame Shinkiro!
Its Absolute Defense
Field is the strongest
protective shield
system in the world.
Ah!
This could be a problem.
[GINO] What are your orders,
Prince Schneizel?
If we fire, the Empress will--
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hmm.
We could just hang back
and wait them out.
There's something
strange about this.
[KANON]
Uh?
[SCHNEIZEL] Why did Zero choose
this time to show up in front.
[ZERO]
How pathetic, Xing-ke.
You were betrayed by
your own countrymen,
and you couldn't even
save one little girl.
Do you get it now?
You need me.
I'm the only ally
you can rely on.
I'll never be subordinate
to you, Zero.
[ZERO]
Subordinate? No.
You have the potential to
lead your entire nation!
They need deliverance.
Your empress.
And all the helpless people
of the Chinese Federation!
They're crying out for it!
[XING-KE]
You think your Knightmare
can turn the tide
of this battle?
Not at all.
The tide of a war is determined
by strategy, not tactics.
[gasps]
[RADIO ANNOUCER]
Emergency alert!
Riots have broken
out in Shanghai!
Street riots?!
[RIOTERS yelling]
--[BOMBER A] Damn you!
--[BOMBER B] You'll pay for this
They're rioting in Shanghai?
[CHINA DECK B]
It's not just Shanghai.
Shou Xian, Beijing, Burma,
Jakarata, Islamabad...
And there are 14 other areas
that we're still confirming.
People are rising up everywhere!
Rebellions breaking
out simultaneously?
Yes, they're broadcasting
a communication
between Zero and
the High Eunuchs.
Communication?
So they were conspiring
without informing us.
Can you run it?
[CECILE]
Yes.
[ZHAO HAO]
The empress is merely a system.
[XIA WANG] There are plenty
of others to replace her.
[ZERO] And what
about the common people
you've sworn to protect?
[ZHAO HAO] Zero, when you
walk down the street,
do you worry about
stepping on the ants?
[XIA WANG] Indeed, masters and
commoners will always breed.
[CHENG ZHONG]
Like insects.
Heh. Thanks to the Empress,
the High Eunuchs are now
firmly cast as the villains.
You mean... you planned
on their betrayal?
He couldn't have caused this;
it's happening too fast.
Unless he made use of someone
else's plan already in place.
[ZERO]
Correct!
I stole another strategy
of yours as well.
We start a coup and
the people rise up!
In other words...
We're not trapped here
without reinforcements!
We do have reinforcements.
The starving masses of this
land are backup we needed.
Then we can take
the offensive...
And strike!
The Black Knights are
to be annihilated.
She's just as tough
as I expected.
[C.C.]
No!
[ANYA gasps]
What is this?!
[C.C.]
So, that's what you did!
[CHIBA]
Mm? What's that?
[ANYA groaning]
[ASAHINA]
Now's our chance!
[ANYA gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Anya, no!
This is the Tristan! I'm
moving in to cover Mordred!
[BLACK KNIGHTS yell]
Push 'em back now!
[BRIT DECK A]
Fools!
Deploying their ground forces
at this point in the battle?
[BRIT DECK B]
If we bomb them from the air,
we'll destroy them.
[SCHNEIZEL]
No, we're withdrawing.
[NINA]
Huh?
Nations aren't dirt and they're
not systems. They're people.
The High Eunuchs have
lost the people's support,
they're no longer qualified
to join us as representatives
of the Chinese Federation.
[SUZAKU]
Yes, Your Highness.
[FUTABA] The Avalon and
the Knights of the Round
are withdrawing!
[OHGI sighs]
[LELOUCH] Yes, I thought
that's what you'd do, Brother.
However...
What do you think the Emperor
would have done Kanon?
Forget it. I was
just musing a bit.
[ZHAO HAO screams]
[XING-KE] So, Prince Schneizel
has abandoned you.
So much for your titles.
Don't hurt us!
We'll give up our power.
Whatever you want!
[XING-KE] Still worried
about your own skin?
--[XING-KE grunting]
--[HIGH EUNUCHS gasping]
[LELOUCH]
Where is Kallen Kouzuki?!
[XIANG-LIN sighs]
That's the Guren's pilot.
She was classified as a
P.O.W. and transferred out.
What?!
The High Eunuchs handed
her over as a favor
to the Knight of Seven.
To Suzaku?!
[LELOUCH] So, you're trying to
take everything away from me,
even Kallen. But that's
not going to happen.
I promised that I'd come
for her, and I will.
Nothing will stop me,
not even you.
[BARTLEY]
Where is this place?
I thought we were going to meet
in the Britannian homeland.
And besides, this was by
direct order of the emperor.
[V.V.] Yes. As requested.
In your attempt to recreate
C.C.'s power, you
enhanced Lord Jeremiah.
In light of your 'efforts' I
felt we should call you in.
You see, I need some
final adjustments.
You're really the only
logical choice for this,
and in any case...
You should be pleased;
it's a great honor for you!
[XING-KE]
Is this all right for you?
[EMPRESS]
Uh. Well...
[XING-KE]
Uh?
I was finally able to leave
the Forbidden City,
uh, and now... I mean...
This doesn't mean it's
"the end." It's just...
I shall protect you in
the future, as well.
Until the very end of time.
It's so strange. I'm so happy!
I'm so happy, and yet...
[EMPRESS cries]
Zero, we need to let the world
know that the Empress's
betrothal to the
Britannian Prince is off.
[ZERO]
That's true.
And the best way to do that
is to have her marry
someone from our side.
A member of a Japanese
family would be perfect.
[EMPRESS]
Uh?!
[LELOUCH]
Hm. That's tastelessly obvious,
but a smart move all the same.
We can have her marry Tohdoh.
Even Tamaki would do.
If you'd like, I can draw up a
list of suitable candidates--
[KAGUYA]
But you mustn't!
Lady Kaguya, this is a political
maneuver, it isn't personal.
You're wrong, it is personal.
It's a simple question of love!
She has a point.
[LELOUCH]
Mm?
We're at war;
lives are at stake!
Hey, you're pushin' it, buddy.
Buddy?! I am a staff officer!
[laughs]
[growls]
[DIETHARD]
Zero, what's your decision?
[KAGUYA] You understand,
Master Zero, don't you?!
[ZERO]
Well...
Zero! Listen,
about yesterday. Hm?
Are you guys still
in conference?
[ZERO]
No, let's go.
[DIETHARD]
Zero! This is vital!
[LELOUCH]
Tamaki's issue is also vital.
I never thought C.C.
would object to this.
I could easily use my Geass
to make Xing-ke and the
others go along with this.
So, what's the problem?
[TAMAKI] Of course, I'm worried
about Kallen, too, y'know.
But, uh I still need you to deal
with my current position here...
If the Black Knights
don't pull together,
we've got problems, right?
But if things stay like this,
I won't get any respect
from the new guys.
[ZERO]
Tamaki...
You get the picture, cause
you're like my best buddy,
aren't ya?!
Uh, Lulu. Do you have a minute?
[LELOUCH]
Yeah, sure, what's up?
Well, it's about Prez's
graduation event, remember?
If I talk about it in class,
Rivalz'll blab to her.
[LELOUCH]
Maybe it's better
just to let her decide for
herself what she wants to do.
[SHIRLEY]
I guess...
Uh, Shirley! Can I
ask you something?
[SHIRLEY]
Mm-hm.
[TAMAKI] Dammit! Every time
ya try to talk to this guy,
he disappears.
The thing is, there's
this couple that just has
to split up, but I can't
convince anyone else.
[SHIRLEY]
Hm. Do they wanna split up?
No, it's a political issue.
Uh! I mean, family politics,
y'know their parents and all.
[SHIRLEY]
Then don't!
[LELOUCH]
Don't what?
[SHIRLEY] Don't break them up!
Love is power!
When you love someone,
that has incredible power!
You think about them
all day long.
You write poetry with bad
rhymes, knit mufflers!
You feel like you can fly,
and that's only the beginning!
And I've always felt like-- Uh!
That is... What about you Lulu?
Haven't you ever felt that way
for someone important to you?
[LELOUCH gasps]
She's right. I have.
I was trying to recreate the
whole world for Nunnally's sake.
Passion has the power to change
the whole entire world!
That's the truth,
isn't it, Shirley?
Thanks, Shirley. I'm really
glad I talked to you.
Really?! Cause passion's very--
[dial tone]
Ah! He'll never change!
Why do I waste my time?!
[ZERO] Your Majesty!
Your future belongs to you.
You decide your own fate.
Zero...
Oh, I knew you'd understand!
But we need to establish
a position of power!
[ZERO] The human heart is
the source of all our power!
That's why the people rose up
against the High Eunuchs,
and why the Black Knights
fight like titans!
We fight with the power
of our hearts!
Ah, yes, you got that right!
Power of the heart, is that it?
Zero, I'm starting to
see what kind of man
dwells behind that mask.
[ZERO] The path
ahead of us is arduous.
[XING-KE] That's precisely why
tomorrow belongs to us alone!
[SHIRLEY] Hm, Lulu has really
been acting strange lately.
One minute he's his usual self,
the next he's weirdly nice.
Like a completely different p--
[LELOUCH]
Uh!
[SHIRLEY]
Huh? Lulu?
[LELOUCH]
Hi! You need something?
[SHIRLEY]
I told you earlier
I was going to bring back
these gardening books.
Ah, of course, that's right.
[SAYOKO]
This isn't good.
If she sees the panel
before it closes,
she'll know about the
underground control center!
What's up? Are you hiding
something there?
[SAYOKO] I can't let her see it!
I've got to stop her!
Shirley!
Lulu?
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[ZERO]
We will find Kallen,
but I need to return
to Area 11 first.
[C.C.]
And the Chinese Federation?
[LELOUCH] There are still some
opposing factions there...
but they'll be no match
for Xing-ke and Tohdoh
now that the people
are on our side.
Besides you want to see it, too.
The power of the human heart.
[C.C.]
The little devil grows up, huh?
And you're still a witch.
In any case, this gets
us back on track
so we can hit them at
their deepest level.
[C.C.]
The religious order?
[LELOUCH] The ones that
are trying to create warriors
with the Geass power.
If we can control the order,
then I can surpass the
emperor in terms of Geass.
[C.C.] However, the very
existence of the order
has been concealed from
the human world.
They change locations when
a new leader is named,
so it's almost impossible
to track them.
[LELOUCH] But you're
certain they're based
in the Chinese Federation right
now, somewhere within reach?
Yes, according to V.V.,
the one that replaced
me as their leader.
But this is a vast country.
Even that guy Rolo doesn't know
where their base is, right?
So, how are you
going to find it?
[LELOUCH] That's why I took
over the Chinese Federation.
[C.C.]
Hm?
[LELOUCH] The flow of goods,
power supplies, communications:
the order must leave
traces of its existence.
You're using the power of
the whole nation to find them?
[LELOUCH] As you said,
"it's a vast country."
You're to remain here C.C.
If you find any clues
on the order, contact me.
Yes, I understand.
[LELOUCH] This place,
are you sure it's safe?
[ROLO]
It's an O.S.I. facility...
Just consider that it may as
well belong to you and I.
Ah!
Welcome home, brother!
It's good to see you, Rolo.
Sayoko, did anything change
while I was away
on this mission?
Nothing of immediate concern.
I noted all the details
in the designated file.
[ROLO] So, you'll be staying
here for quite a while now,
isn't that right, Lelouch?
[LELOUCH] Yes, I have to develop
some effective countermeasures
for the Knights of the Round.
The Lancelot's bad enough,
and we certainly don't need
the Tristan and the Mordred
getting in our way again.
[ROLO] It would be a pleasure
to back you up in my Vincent.
[LELOUCH sighs] I told you
not to behave like that.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Shirley, are you okay?
Look, Lulu about what happened
with us yesterday...
Yesterday?
[gasps]
Morning, Lelouch Lamperouge.
[ROLO gasps]
It's Anya, the Knight of Six!
Hey, we've been
waiting for you!
You're the Vice-President,
right? This is an honor--
[RIVALZ]
Don't be so formal.
[GINO]
Oh, right.
Anyway, we've both just enrolled
here at Ashford. And...
While we're here, we insist that
our social status be ignored.
They said they wanted
the experience
of being ordinary students.
So I'm teaching them
how to talk normal.
[GINO] I am really lookin'
forward to this... Old Man.
Uh. Right.
[LELOUCH] Gino Weinberg.
Anya Alstreim.
What are they thinking?!
What are they up to?!
The Knights of the Round have
not only come to Ashford,
they've joined the
student council?!
I thought no one but the OSI and
Suzaku would look at me as some
kind of bait to capture C.C...
I doubt this is part of Suzaku's
operation, but the emperor
of Britannia might be feeding
them the information.
If they realize I'm Zero,
then Nunnally is in danger!
Somehow, I have to find out what
these two are really up to!