[SECRETARY GENERAL]
Open fire!
Gloucesters?!
They're supposed
to be in Serupham!
Shoddy oversized
imitation Knightmares!
They would've been wise to
surrender from the start.
[ALL yelping]
What?!
So, Cornelia, a single
unit, did this?!
Another victory.
Area 18 has been established.
[DALTON] My Lady, about
our next course of action...
Sorry to have you clean up after
my foolish younger brother.
[DALTON]
Please don't apologize, milady.
We live to serve, and
our place is with you.
[CORNELIA]
Ha.
Do you think Area 11
needs our usual treatment?
[DALTON]
Yes, milady.
Good.
[CORNELIA] I'll drive you
into the open, Zero.
Clovis will be avenged.
[LELOUCH]
I'm back.
Welcome home, Lelouch.
I'm so glad. I was worried.
I'm assuming you
ate out tonight,
judging from your appearance.
[NUNNALLY]
Thank goodness!
I thought maybe you'd
gotten caught up
in all the uproar
caused by that man Zero.
I tried calling you, but you
didn't answer your cell phone.
I wanted to tell you Miss C.C.'s
been waiting for you, as well.
[gasps]
C.C.?
[NUNNALLY giggles]
Your friend goes by such an
unusual name. Only her initials.
[LELOUCH]
Yeah...
I was just wondering,
is C.C. your girlfriend?
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
He made a promise about
our future together.
Right?
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[NUNNALLY] A future together?
You mean marriage?
No!
No, that isn't what
she was talkin' about.
It's like, uh...
She's kidding around.
[C.C.]
No, I'm not.
Well, you're certainly doing
this sooner than most.
But everyone's
different, aren't they?
So I suppose it
isn't that strange,
and if you feel like
you're ready for-- Uh.
[LELOUCH]
Oh, C.C., look what you've done.
You're soaking wet.
C'mon, let's get you
to the bathroom
into a dry change of clothes.
Nunnally, stay here, and I'll
clean that up in a minute.
And she was kidding
before. Kidding!
Just a dumb joke, that's all!
[LELOUCH]
Who are you?
She said my name. I'm C.C.
That's not what I meant.
Why aren't you--
Supposed to be dead?
[C.C.]
So...
...do you like the power
that I gave you?
[LELOUCH]
As I thought. It was you.
[C.C.]
Dissatisfied?
[LELOUCH]
On the contrary, I'm grateful.
It allows me to speed up
my schedule tremendously,
which is a huge help.
[C.C.]
Your schedule?
[LELOUCH] Yes, my schedule
for obliterating Britannia.
I'd have had to wait much longer
before I could've made
the initial move.
You believe you can destroy it
simply by using that power?
[LELOUCH] I intended to
do it without this power.
I just knew that he'd turn out
to be a fascinating guy.
[LELOUCH]
What will you do now?
I'm sure the military
is after you.
[C.C.] Not the entire military,
only a small faction of it.
So it shouldn't be difficult
to find a hiding place.
[C.C.]
I can make do here.
What?! You expect to stay here?!
[C.C.] A gentleman would
sleep on the floor.
[LELOUCH]
Don't joke around.
[C.C.] My being caught would
cause trouble for you, too.
[LELOUCH]
It's dangerous to stay together.
[C.C.] If I wander the
streets, they'll find me.
This isn't about you.
It's my situation.
[C.C.]
I hate stubbornness!
[LELOUCH grunts]
[LELOUCH] You sure take
things casually, don't you?
How did you manage
to survive before this?
What did you do before now?
And what's the deal with that
so-called "contract" you spoke--
[C.C.]
Goodnight, Lelouch.
[CECILE]
Fukushima, Kochi, Hiroshima.
This has been the
seventh occurrence
since that man named
Zero raised his head.
[LLOYD] It seems that the other
groups are following his lead
and putting up a valiant fight.
[CECILE] And now suspicions
about that "Orange" thing
have cost Margrave
Jeremiah his command.
[LLOYD] Maybe he wasn't
good enough. Thanks to him,
connections between the
police and administration
are screwed up. It's made
a fine mess for us, as well.
[KUSAKABE]
Help them, Tohdoh!
Zero has thrown the
Britannians into chaos!
Now's the time for us in
the Japan Liberation Front
to make our stand!
[TOHDOH]
Calm down!
The information of Kyoto
giving the Guren MK-2 to Zero
hasn't been confirmed.
If we pay too much
attention to Zero,
we may trip ourselves up.
[C.C.] So, what did "Orange"
turn out to be, anyway?
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[C.C.]
Well?
You know, for someone who isn't
willing to answer any questions,
you certainly do
ask a lot of them.
If you don't want to
answer my questions,
you don't have to.
Just as I don't.
[sighs]
There is no "Orange,"
it's something I made up.
But... the more they claim
to be comrades of like mind,
the easier it is to divide them
with the thorns of suspicion.
[C.C.]
Hm.
[C.C.] Everyone on Earth
is looking for you.
Because of you, the world
is going through an upheaval.
So.
Is this it? Is this what
you wanted to see?
[LELOUCH]
No.
This uproar is simply
a means to an end.
The world is destined to
descend into greater chaos.
[JUSTICE OFFICIAL]
Case number 107,
Private Suzaku Kururugi,
Area 11 military forces.
In the murder of His
Highness Prince Clovis,
you are no longer a suspect
and hereby set free
due to lack of evidence.
What happened? I'm free.
[GIRL]
Outta the way, please!
Look out below!
Uh... are you all right?
I'm sorry!
I wasn't aware you were down
here until I had leaped!
Well, don't worry.
I wasn't expecting a girl
to come falling outta the sky
and into my arms, either.
Oh, my!
Huh? Is there something wrong?
Yes! There is something wrong!
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[GIRL] The truth is,
bad guys are chasing me.
So considering
the circumstances,
could you help me, please?
[KEWELL] We must get rid
of this "Orange" character
before Princess Cornelia
assumes her new post!
Now the loyalty of us purebloods
is being called into question.
[SIGNALMAN] Are the reports
we've been hearing true?
Lord Jeremiah was bribed?
Do you know what
this "Orange" means?
[SIGNALMAN]
Uh...
[KNIGHT A]
In any case,
Lord Jeremiah is
definitely hiding something.
Saying he can't recall anything.
Bartley offered the same excuse.
[VILLETTA] Lord Jeremiah's
memory is muddled.
Exactly like those
of the men in Shinjuku
whose Sutherlands were stolen.
And...
[gasps]
[GIRL] We haven't introduced
ourselves yet, have we?
My name is...
[GIRL]
Euphy!
Euphy?
[EUPHY]
Yes.
My name's--
[EUPHY]
Don't tell me!
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
'Cause I already know it.
You're a celebrity.
Son of Prime Minister
Genbu Kururugi,
Private Suzaku Kururugi.
[SUZAKU]
Hm.
You lied before. There's no
one chasing you at all, right?
[EUPHY]
Meow!
What?
[EUPHY]
Meow, meow!
Aw, does a kitty's paw hurt?
Oh.
Meow, meow, meow!
[meows]
Meow, meow.
[SUZAKU]
Hm.
[SUZAKU chuckles]
[EUPHY]
Oh, my.
[LLOYD]
We're running late.
I hope he's still
waiting for us.
Considering the charge,
did they really release him?
Yes, they had no evidence.
I'm sure they put him
through the third degree
because of that
Zero incident. Huh?
What? Why is he--?
[gasps]
Do you have trouble with cats?
Hm. I like them fine, however...
[hisses]
Hm. The attraction isn't mutual.
I think unrequited love is
the mark of a kind person.
Oh!
[SUZAKU]
Uh.
[EUPHEMIA]
The kitty ran away.
Mm, Euphy...
Why did you tell me
that lie when we met?
Do you ask because
you're concerned about me?
Huh? Um, of course.
Good! Then you can
accompany me some more!
C'mon, it'll be fun!
[EUPHY] You know, being here
is just like being in Britannia.
I feel right at home.
[SUZAKU]
Are you from the Homeland?
[EUPHY]
Uh-huh!
I was a student there
up until last week.
[SUZAKU] Last week?
So, what are you doing now?
By student, do you
mean high school?
You can go sightseeing
any time, can't you?
[EUPHY giggles]
[EUPHY]
You ask a lotta questions.
[SUZAKU]
Uh. Sorry...
[EUPHY] Oh! No, I didn't
mean it like that!
You see... today is the
last day of my vacation.
I wanted to see as much
of Area 11 as I could,
because I'd like to know
what kind of place it is.
[SUZAKU] Well, you
didn't need me for that.
[EUPHEMIA] No. I'm glad
I could see with you.
[SUZAKU]
Is that right?
[EUPHY]
Suzaku...
Would you mind taking me
to one more place, please?
Your wish is my command,
milady. Where to?
[EUPHY]
Take me to Shinjuku.
[gasps]
[EUPHY]
Suzaku Kururugi.
Please escort me there.
[KALLEN]
Lelouch?
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[KALLEN]
Do you have a minute?
[LELOUCH]
Mh-hm. What is it?
[KALLEN] About that
phone call the other day...
Phone call?
Yeah... You know, when you
and I were in the bathroom.
[LELOUCH]
Uh-huh.
[KALLEN] Can you find out
what the caller I.D. was?
I want to contact
that person again.
It was a school phone.
So I'm no sure, sor-- Uh!
I see.
Makes sense.
I should've known.
[LELOUCH]
That girl.
[KALLEN]
Uh.
What?
Is there something wro-- Uh!
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
No way...
[KALLEN]
Excuse me.
What're you doing?
Ah. What indeed.
[BARTLEY] To think I'd return
to the Homeland like this.
I wish I'd never involved
that damned girl.
[LELOUCH]
Are you insane?!
You can't go walkin' around!
[C.C.]
Don't act strict with me.
I never leave the school
grounds, so it's fine.
It's not! You can't do as you
like here. You don't belong!
[C.C.]
I don't belong anywhere.
Hm? What's with her?
Oh. Is she doing
it again today?
[C.C.]
Again?
[LELOUCH] She's going to be
markin' the wall like that
every day, because I used my
Geass on her to make her do it.
[C.C.]
Geass?
[LELOUCH]
The name of the power I have.
That's what I heard when
we first made contact.
[C.C.]
Hm.
You're testing
how long it lasts?
I need to know the specs
of my weapon, don't I?
So behave, or I'll
try it on you.
Would it work... on me?
[LELOUCH]
Uh.
Oh, relax.
You and I are in this together.
I won't do anything to endanger
us or our unique partnership.
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
[SUZAKU] The Shinjuku ghetto.
Ruined again.
The residents were
starting to return, too.
[OTAKU A] Man, they didn't
use R-G on the Elevens.
I figured they wouldn't.
[OTAKU B]
Hey, look!
Those are marks from hummer
rounds. Get a clear shot of it!
[OTAKU A] Say "cheese"!
Got it! Okay, me next!
[JEREMIAH]
This is accurate?
This information about Zero?
[SIGNALMAN] Yes, sir.
Lord Kewell contacted me.
Right.
Set up a cordon around Shinjuku
ghetto sector 4 at once!
Cordon sector 4, roger.
Okay, ball's in your
court now, Lord Kewell.
[BOTH gasp]
[VILLETTA] I wanted to put be
through to Lord Jeremiah,
but it appears that
you're too busy now.
Get out of here, you
damn Britannian bastards!
[SUZAKU]
Stay here!
How dare a lowly
Eleven speak like--
[TAMAKI] Don't call me an
Eleven! I'm Japanese!
[OTAKU B] Wrong, you seem to
forget that you people lost!
You're nothing but a beaten dog!
You racist pig!
[SUZAKU]
Stop, please! No violence!
[TAMAKI]
Stay outta this!
You're that...
Are you... Suzaku Kururugi?
[MINAMI]
The guy who killed Clovis?
[YOSHIDA] No, idiot.
It was Zero who killed him.
[TAMAKI] Tch. This guy's
nothing more than a slave.
Big deal, you're an honorary
Britannian. Nobody cares.
You sold your pride,
your people, your soul,
yet you call
yourself Japanese?!!
No, you're wrong! I--
[TAMAKI]
I am not wrong!
You stinkin' Britannian lap dog!
Stop, please!
[groaning]
I warn you, I've been
trained for military combat.
Don't make me fight
against my own people.
[TAMAKI]
Like hell we're "your people"!
[MINAMI]
C'mon, just let it go!
[TAMAKI]
Ugh! Lousy traitor!
[EUPHY]
Suzaku!
Oh, my! Are you okay?
[SUZAKU]
Yeah, I'm all right.
Well, I'm not okay! Just look
at my Prime G and my LX-4!
Why did you wait?!
Dammit, some honorary
citizen you are!
Why'd you let 'em go?!
You shoulda killed them!
What's a few dead Elevens
to a guy like you?!
Who do you think's taken care of
you all of these years anyway?!
[OTAKU A yelps]
I'll not allow you to insult
this man any longer, you oaf!
[LELOUCH]
To use my Geass,
I need to have direct eye
contact with the subject.
Transparent objects like
eyeglasses present no problem.
The effective range is
approximately 270 meters,
and the subject appears
to have no memory
of events before, during,
or after the power is used.
I think this is due to
damage caused by the Geass
interfering with the
brain of the subject.
Also, if the signal's
optical, I can reflect it.
In the short time you've
had it, you've learned a lot.
[LELOUCH]
My opponent is an empire
that controls more than
one-third of the entire world.
There's no such thing
as being too careful.
[C.C.] I'd understand
if you were an Eleven,
but you're a Britannian,
aren't you?
This opponent may be
too large and strong
to fight with only
Geass for a weapon.
[LELOUCH]
Is it good to be strong?
[SUZAKU]
Is it bad to be weak?
Back then, when I was ten,
the world seemed like
such a terribly sad place.
A world without any hope at all.
[LELOUCH]
Starvation.
[SUZAKU]
Disease.
Filth. Decay.
Racism.
Constant war and terrorism.
Living in a
never-ending cycle of hate.
[LELOUCH]
Rat's running in a wheel.
[SUZAKU]
The cycle must be broken.
Somebody has to do it.
How idealistic.
[SUZAKU]
Of course, it's doubtful
that the one who does it will
make all the bad things go away.
[LELOUCH]
I'm not that arrogant. And so...
No one should lose more
of the people they love.
At least, a world without war.
[C.C.]
And to have this utopia you'd...
How would you do it?
It's simple.
When somebody wins...
...the fighting will end.
[C.C.]
Somebody?
[SUZAKU] I don't know
how you would do it.
But if I stop trying,
then my father's death
will have been in vain.
The Prime Minister's death?
My own father died
because he had to sacrifice
his life in that war!
[explosion]
[EUPHY gasps]
[KEWELL]
Jeremiah!
You're going to pay for letting
Prince Clovis' murderer go free!
Kewell, you dirty coward!
That sighting of Zero
was a lie, wasn't it?!
[KEWELL] We have to
wipe away our disgrace
before Princess Cornelia
takes up her post here.
This is how we keep
our officials honest.
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Miss Cecile!
[CECILE]
It's dangerous here! Get in!
The purebloods are
having a silly squabble.
Better get out of here.
Oh, and by the way, what
a shame about your acquittal.
Because now you'll have
to work for me again.
[SUZAKU]
Wait, please!
Isn't this an opportunity
to gather battle data
for the Lancelot?
[CECILE]
Uh?
[LLOYD]
Oh, ho...
[EUPHY]
Suzaku...
I'm sorry, Euphy, we
have to say goodbye here.
I need to do this. I think I can
stop them with the Lancelot.
I have to try. I--
I must!
Damn! It's four against one!
Cowards!
[KEWELL]
Don't worry, Jeremiah.
We'll say you died in battle.
Your family's name
won't be disgraced.
You're serious then?
You actually intend to kill me?!
Kewell!
[KEWELL]
Silence, Orange!
We serve the imperial family!
Why else would we be here?!
All... hail... Britannia!
[KEWELL]
Wha--?!
[SUZAKU] Stop it! You're
all Britannian soldiers!
That's him. It's that
honorary Britannian.
The advanced weapon! Lancelot!
[KEWELL] What business does
the Special Corps want here?!
Interlopers will die!
[SUZAKU]
No!
[SUZAKU] I can't stand by and
ignore this senseless battle!
Oh my god. They've
perfected the MVSs.
Too late! I won't back down!
We're on the same side!
Suzaku Kururugi... is saving me?
We can at least kill Orange!
Lord Jeremiah!
Villetta, thanks!
[SUZAKU]
Still wanna fight?
Men, stand down.
[VILLETTA]
Kewell?
[SUZAKU]
You understand, then?
[KEWELL]
I'm using a chaos mine.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
No! Stop it now!
What?
[SUZAKU grunting]
That honorary Britannian...
He risked his life for...
[EUPHY] Everyone, lower
your weapons at once!
[EUPHEMIA]
In my name, I command you!
It... can't be.
I am Euphemia Li
Britannia of the empire,
and the third princess
of the royal family!
[gasps]
Euphy?
[EUPHEMIA] I'm assuming
command here! Now fall back!
It is her. It's the princess.
Did you know it was her, Lloyd?
[LLOYD]
Uh-huh.
But she's been a
student up until now
and hasn't made her
public debut yet.
We... we're truly...
We're truly sorry,
Your Highness!
[SUZAKU]
My lady!
[EUPHEMIA]
Uh?
I had no idea who you were.
Please forgive me, Princess!
Suzaku, you and I bear
a similar deep pain.
You have lost your father
as I have lost my brother.
[gasps]
Will you let me help
you in your quest
to ensure that no one ever
again has to suffer the loss
of a loved one
on the battlefield?
[SUZAKU] Yes! I'm...
unworthy of your kindness.
[CORNELIA]
I heard what you did, Euphemia.
You shouldn't be so reckless.
[EUPHEMIA] I know, sister.
Forgive me. But...
[CORNELIA] You will
address me as viceroy here,
sub-viceroy Euphemia.
Because we're sisters, we need
to follow a stricter protocol.
Yes. I understand.
[CORNELIA]
Heh.
Now then, give me your report.
Yes. Milady, the first order
of business is a welcome party
we've arranged for
Your Highness and-- Uh!
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
[CORNELIA]
Sloppy. Senile. Corrupt.
Where is Zero?! I want the enemy
of the empire caught! Get Zero!
[LELOUCH]
Uh?
[SUZAKU] I'll be joining
the student body here
at Ashford Academy
beginning today.
My name is Suzaku Kururugi.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[LELOUCH]
Yes. I understand. I'm lying.
To Shirley and Rivalz
and the others.
Even to Suzaku and Nunnally.
But there's no goin' back now.
I can't turn back.
As long as C.C. and I are
bound by our "contract,"
I have to keep at this.
Beause I don't wanna
lie to myself any more.