[C.C.]
Lelouch, a Britannian youth,
has been given a god-like power
by the mysterious
young woman, C.C.
Geass.
The absolute power to compel
anyone to follow any order.
For the sake of his
younger sister, Nunnally,
Lelouch plots to destroy
the Holy Britannian Empire.
Meanwhile, his best friend from
childhood, Suzaku Kururugi,
has established himself
as an honorary Britannian
within the Empire.
At this point, their lives
are already intertwined
and their destinies
predetermined
with inevitable outcomes.
I never left the Tokyo
settlement before!
This is my first time!
I'm sure you wish Lelouch could
have come with us, don't you?
[SHIRLEY gasps]
Don't be so shy.
Tonight, we can stay up
all night talking.
Let's tell each other which
boys we like from school.
Then you'll probably
have a lot to talk about,
right, Ms. President?
Who can say?
[gasps]
[MILLY]
Nina, it's all right.
There are lots of Britannian
tourists at Lake Kawaguchi,
so security's fine.
Don't be afraid.
It's not the ghettos.
Yes, but--
We'll be with you
the whole time.
We won't leave your
side for a second.
Th-Thanks.
[ZERO] What are you
waiting for? Come in.
As of now, this place
will be our hideout.
[OHGI]
So...
...you think joining up
with us is a good idea?
[ZERO]
Yes. We're comrades, after all.
[MINAMI]
Holy cow!
[TAMAKI]
So, what is this, huh?
D'you mind if I ask
how you came by this?
[ZERO] I borrowed it from
a rather libertine nobleman
who indulges my requests.
[OHGI] You asked for it?
Just like that?
[ZERO] Don't worry.
No strings attached.
[YOSHIDA]
It's huge.
Check it out, it's
got a second story.
[KALLEN]
On the other hand,
no one would expect us
in something like this.
[MINAMI]
It's even got a TV.
[NEWSCASTER] How's are
things looking at the scene?
[MINAMI]
Huh?
--I'm here in front of
--[KALLEN] What's this?
the Lake Kawaguchi
Convention Center Hotel.
The hotel jackers have
identified themselves
as the Japan Liberation Front.
Members of the Sakuradite
allocation meeting,
most notably, Chairman
James, were taken hostage,
as well as several tourists
and hotel employees.
This footage was taken
by the perpetrators.
In it, you can clearly
see Chairman James,
including some students.
From the student council.
[ZERO]
Hm?
[REPORTER] The leader of
the group claims to be
Lt. Colonel Kusakabe of the
now-defunct Japanese military.
Agh! That imbecile!
Sakuradite, an
essential component
in the manufacture of high
temperature superconductors,
is a vital strategic resource
that directly affects
world security.
Area 11 is the largest
producer of this material,
providing 70% of the
world's total supply.
Here at the yearly national
meeting of Sakuradite producers,
it will be determined how this
resource will be distributed
among the world's nations.
It's no exaggeration
to say that the outcome
determines the balance
of global power
between Britannia
and other countries.
It is believed that the
terrorists are using
world interest in
the annual gathering
to their advantage by carrying
out this violent hotel takeover.
I'm Kusakabe of the
Japan Liberation Front.
This stand we're taking
is for the freedom of Japan
and our countrymen!
Even though you
are not soldiers,
you are still Britannians!
You are the ones who
rule and oppress us!
Sit still, be quiet,
and you'll be fine.
If you don't--!
Lulu.
[TAMAKI]
So, they've made their move.
They're easily the biggest
anti-Britannian force in Japan.
And now their pride's hurt.
Because of us?
Maybe.
[TAMAKI] I don't know whether to
feel happy or sad about that.
Because they're all
gonna end up dead.
[LELOUCH]
Rivalz?
Uh! Lelouch, I've-- Huh?
[LELOUCH]
This is Lelouch.
Please leave a message
after the beep.
What the hell's he doing
at a time like this?!
[LELOUCH]
I know. But...
[STAFF OFFICER A] All bridges
connecting to the hotel,
with the exception of the main
one, have been destroyed.
Our attempted approaches
from air and water
have been unsuccessful.
There's only one route left
that will allow us to develop
a possible hostage rescue plan.
The main utilities tunnel
running directly beneath
the convention center hotel.
Basically, we would go
in through this route,
destroy the foundation block,
and submerge the hotel.
Since the tunnel was also built
to handle supply deliveries,
it should be able to
accommodate Sutherlands.
Even if the enemy
has taken precautions,
it should be no problem.
[PILOT A]
Go.
[STAFF OFFICER A] They've been
using sub-standard weaponry,
so we'll have no
trouble evading them.
[PILOT 1]
Enemy detected!
As expected, they're moving
through the underground tunnel!
Roger that!
Raikou, secondary start-up!
Both quad-linkage legs locked!
Super electromagnetic shrapnel
cannon voltage, confirmed!
[PILOT A] I think these guys
have Knightmare rifles.
Spread out and
break their ranks.
Super electromagnetic
shrapnel cannon, fire!
[PILOT A]
What?!
[SOLDIER 1]
One shot!
--Yes!
--It works!
The Raikou was
a complete success!
What do you think of
that, Britannian pigs?
Wiped out?!
[STAFF OFFICER A] It looks
as though they've modified
a Glasgow into a linear cannon.
[STAFF OFFICER B] Then there's
no way we can break through.
[STAFF OFFICER C]
What do we do now?
If we release the political
prisoners as they demand--
We can't show
weakness to terrorists!
But Princess Euphemia, she's...
Yes, I know.
Thus far, it appears
that none of them
have discovered that fact.
If they learn that Princess
Euphemia is among the hostages,
they'll undoubtedly use
her as a bargaining chip.
She went there just to observe,
therefore she isn't registered
along with the other guests.
[C.C.] Yes. Yes, I understand.
I'll do well this time.
I'll try to look out for him,
but I'm not his guardian.
[SUZAKU] Can't the Special
Corps offer any assistance
with the rescue operation?
[LLOYD] I've already asked them,
but we're an irregular unit,
and they don't acknowledge
our chain of command.
Besides...
It's too risky to entrust
the operation to an Eleven,
is that right?
Yet I'm sure you're aware
that Princess Cornelia
is very discriminating about
Britannians and Numbers.
So the Japanese still aren't
being accepted enough
into your structure?
If that were true, then
what point would there be
in even having an honorary
Britannian system?
[REPORTER] Sir, did
your daughter appear...
[MINAMI]
Where do you want this?
Over there, by
the driver's seat.
[YOSHIDA] Hey! What
about these boxes here?
[SHIRLEY'S DAD]
She was only sightseeing!
Shirley is still a student.
But these criminals
act indiscriminately.
Savages! I want
to know if Shir--
I want to know if my
daughter's all right!
She hasn't done
anything wrong!
[REPORTER]
All he's asking...
[LELOUCH] We need to organize
before we fight them again.
It's too soon, though.
We're not ready.
But we can't just sit here
and do nothing, either.
Knowing Cornelia, she'll
sacrifice the hostages.
Then why doesn't
she make her move?
Is it possible?
[KALLEN]
Zero.
What will happen
to the hostages?
[ZERO]
Eventually...
...there will be no reason to
keep those Britannians alive.
Yeah. I'm sure you're right.
[OHGI]
Hey, Zero. I found these.
Should I hand them
out to everyone?
I mean, as far as gear
goes, it looks pretty hip,
but we're just a
resistance group, so--
[ZERO]
Wrong!
We're not a resistance
group. Is that clear?
Well then, what are we?
[ZERO] What we are...
what we're trying to be...
...are knights for justice.
[COMM 1] Attention all sniper
teams. Situation is "hold."
All team commanders, confirm...
[CECILE] Those teenage
hostages are friends of yours
from school, aren't they?
They're still negotiating,
so let's not give up hope.
[SUZAKU]
I have faith in the system.
I prefer the logic of systems
to individualist emotions.
Uh. Miss Cecile, look!
[CECILE]
Huh?
LooK!
[SUZAKU]
That's...
What are they gonna do to him?!
Oh, no...
Don't do it!
[SUZAKU]
No!
Our demands have
gone unanswered.
Therefore, we will throw
one hostage from the roof
every 30 minutes until
our terms are met.
For the sake of the hostages,
negotiations better
be in good faith!
[DARLTON] This is their
warning? Barbarians.
[GUILFORD]
For now, we could negotiate
just to get the women
and children out--
Forget it!
If you give in to their
conditions even once
then you're simply
legitimizing terrorism!
Then do we use force?
We would pursue that
course of action
after we secure the safety
of Princess Euphemia.
[grunts]
[CORNELIA]
Euphy... I...
[VICE SOLDIER 1]
Viceroy! It's Zero!
We just received a
message from Zero.
[DIETHARD]
What?
What do you mean van
three was stolen by Zero?
What the hell was Gibson
doing all the while?
He said that when he
realized what was happening,
it was too late.
[DIETHARD]
Ugh. Then where's van three now?
Driving straight
toward the military.
[DIETHARD]
Huh?
[COMM 2] We confirm.
It's Zero! Should we open fire?
[COMM 3]
No, just stand by.
We'll capture him
after he's surrounded.
[OHGI]
Hey...
When Zero went off
about "justice" earlier,
what do you think he meant?
[KALLEN]
Dunno.
But we may die first
before we find out.
It seems all of our escape
routes have been cut off.
[YOSHIDA] I'm just wondering,
why didn't we use that trailer?
[SUGIYAMA]
Oh, so you want the whole world
to see where we hide out, huh?
[MINAMI]
Point taken.
[INOUE] I don't know
about this Zero character.
You sure we should trust him?
[TAMAKI] No, that's why I
said he looked shifty to me.
But if anything goes wrong,
I'll do somethin' about it.
[LELOUCH]
Cornelia...
Much as I'd love to get you
back right here and now,
you're more useful to me alive.
If you do what I predict,
I won't need to use my Geass.
Well, well, we meet again, Zero.
Are you a member of the
Japan Liberation Front?
Or perhaps you
intend to help us.
Regardless,
our concerns take priority
over yours at the moment.
And so, for the death of
my half-brother, Clovis,
I shall take my
revenge right here!
[ZERO] Cornelia!
Which would you chose?
Clovis, who is dead, or
Euphemia, who is alive?
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
My suspicion's confirmed.
The first task at
hand is completed.
You haven't changed,
dear sister.
You've always doted on
sweet little Euphemia.
That's why you won't
take aggressive action.
Your emotions are
getting in the way.
[ZERO] It's within my power
to save Euphemia for you.
[CORNELIA]
What do you mean?
I have no idea what
you're talking about!
[ZERO] I said that
I'm able to rescue her!
Zero, you say?
Yes, sir. Word came
from the Britannian army.
[COMM 1]
Attention all forces!
Let Zero pass! I repeat,
let Zero pass!
[LELOUCH] Either the
Japan Liberation Front
will accept me as their ally,
or they're going to treat me as
nothing more than a nuisance.
In any event, I highly
doubt that they can't resist
the temptation of meeting
the infamous Zero.
We shall see...
Excellent.
All the operation's preliminary
conditions have been cleared.
[DARLTON]
Viceroy, what are we doing?
[CORNELIA] I believe that
by letting Zero go in,
we can buy some time before
the next hostage is executed.
So... this is our chance.
We can hit them both
at the same time.
Wonderful! I want to thank
you for that lovely order!
[laughing]
[LLOYD] They said you've got
the green light, Lancelot!
You've orders to charge right in
to that linear canon
in the tunnel.
Wait a minute, you mean
they're using him as a decoy
to make an opening for them?
[LLOYD] Yup! Seems like
they'll use the confusion
to send in the royal guard!
"Seems like"?! But Lloyd--!
Miss Cecile.
I'm ready. Please let me do it.
If Lancelot and I are needed,
and we're able to give the
hostages an opportunity
to be saved, then I'll do it.
Even if it means being a decoy.
[CECILE]
Warrant Officer Kururugi,
here is a guideline
for your mission.
According to prime search,
the hostages are located
on the hotel's middle floor
and believed to be locked
inside a food storage room.
Advanced prototype
weapon Z-01 Lancelot
will use the utilities tunnel
to move under the hotel.
Once on site, you will
destroy the foundation block
and submerge the building.
The area with the hostages
should hold out
for eight minutes.
Hostage rescue and
mop-up of the terrorists
will be handled by other units.
You will be using the VARIS
to destroy the foundation.
Set the impact rail to
anti-material level three.
[LLOYD]
The only variable in this
is that pesky linear cannon
waiting for you in the tunnel.
Space is tight in there.
The Lancelot will only
have a 47.8% evasion rate.
Are we really going
through with this?
Yup. Make sure you both pull out
of there before it's too late.
Lancelot might be wrecked,
that would be unacceptable.
[SUZAKU]
"Before it's too late"?
[LLOYD]
Mmmm!
Understood, sir.
[SHIRLEY]
Suzaku.
The president, and Nina and
I are going to Lake Kawaguchi
on Sunday. Wanna join us?
[SUZAKU]
Sorry. I have to work that day.
You do?
Too bad, but I guess
that can't be helped then.
[SUZAKU] But thank
you for inviting me.
I really appreciate it.
I hope all of you
have a great time.
[CECILE] Twelve minutes
to operation start.
Commencing countdown.
[NINA crying]
[NINA]
An Eleven?
[growls] What did you say?!
[NINA cries]
Not Elevens! We are
Japanese, dammit!
Yes, we're aware of that!
Just lay off of her!
Then correct her! We're
not called "Elevens"!
Fine, we'll correct her!
[GUARD] How dare you
speak like that to me!
You three, come with
me to the next room,
and I'll teach you
a real lesson!
[BODYGUARD]
Mh-hm.
I said get up! Now!
[NINA screaming]
Let me go!
[EUPHEMIA]
Stop it!
[GUARD]
Who the hell are you?!
I demand you take me to your
leader right now, understand?!
[GUARD]
What?!
No, Sub-viceroy, please.
You're addressing
Euphemia Li Britannia.
The third princess of
the Britannian Empire.
[ALL gasping]
Are you all right, young lady?
You haven't been hurt?
[NINA gasps]
No.
[ZERO] You have no
intention of joining me?
[KUSAKABE] Remove that mask
and reveal your real face to us.
It's disrespectful not to.
[ZERO]
I understand.
But before I do, I'd like
to ask you something.
What exactly do you hope to
accomplish by this action?
[KUSAKABE]
Gain attention.
I want this country
and the world to know
that the Japanese
aren't dead yet.
[ZERO]
How stale.
[KUSAKABE]
Hm?!
[ZERO] You people are obsolete.
There's no saving you.
What?! Why you arrogant--!
Explain what you
mean by that, Zero.
M.E. boost...
Lancelot, now launching!
[PILOT 1] Reaction confirmed!
One enemy Knightmare!
[PILOT 3] It moves twice
as fast as the others!
[PILOT 2] So what?!
It'll end up like the rest!
Super electromagnetic
shrapnel cannon... Fire!
I warned you
about this, Lloyd!
He doesn't want to play decoy,
he's going for the gold!
[GUARD] I brought the hostage
that I radioed about earlier
for the lieutenant
colonel to see.
She claims that she's
Princess Euphemia.
[KUSAKABE]
Zero!
There's no point
talking any more!
[ZERO]
Die.
[PILOT 2]
Fire!
[gunshots]
[GUARDS gasping]
Colonel!
[ZERO]
Calm yourselves.
Zero.
[ZERO] The colonel and the
others committed suicide
when they realized how
meaningless this operation was.
Euphemia...
You were willing to sacrifice
yourself for the commoners.
You haven't changed.
[EUPHEMIA]
Uh?
What? The ASEEC's Knightmare?
Yes. At the rate it's going,
it'll break through soon.
Huh. Do we dare hold out hope?
Yes!
It can take this level
of destructive force!
That thing broke through
salvo number five!
I can't believe it!
Just don't panic!
Deploy the quad-link free-fire
arm gun, batteries too!
We'll shield this final
defense line with our lives!
Miss Cecile, it's time
for me to use the VARIS.
[CECILE]
No, you could get killed!
There's no room
for me to evade.
I'll risk getting blasted
to take the first shot!
[SOLDIER]
Why, you stinking son of a--
[ZERO] I heard that you're the
sub-viceroy now, Your Highness.
Princess Euphemia Li Britannia.
It's not an appointment
I'm happy with.
[ZERO] No. That's because
Clovis was murdered.
That was my handiwork.
He begged pathetically for
his life to the very end.
He pleaded with the same tongue
that ordered the
deaths of Elevens.
So is that the reason
why you killed my brother?
[ZERO]
No.
Then why?!
[ZERO]
Because Clovis was an offspring
of the Britannian emperor.
That reminds me...
You're one of his
children, too, aren't you?
Use maximum output!
I don't give a damn if
that destroys the guns!
Be prepared to die defending
this spot! Smash him!
It's the Eleven...
[HOSTAGES gasping]
He really did it!
Guilford!
Right!
No way!
[LELOUCH] The white
Knightmare from before!
[gasps]
Euphy!
[SUZAKU]
My friends!
Warrant Officer Kururugi, don't!
[DIETHARD] What about
the cameras in van three?
I told you, Zero took the van--
Well then, let's hope we
pick up a signal from them!
What're you doing, Zero?
Wasn't that part of your plan?
To show us something?
He's all right!
[LLOYD sighs]
I couldn't rescue them.
They're dead.
I failed.
Not again!
We've got it!
[CROWD chattering]
[ZERO] My dear Britannians...
have no fear.
All of the hostages from
the hotel are safe and sound.
I, Zero, return them
to you unharmed.
They're fine!
They're all right!
Of all the brazen audacity!
If we attack you,
those people will quickly become
your hostages, won't they?!
[ZERO]
People!
Fear us, or rally behind
us, as you see fit.
We... are the Black Knights!
Black Knights?
Ironic, isn't it?
The terrorists referring
to themselves as knights.
[ZERO] We of the Black
Knights stand with all those
who have no weapons to wield!
Regardless of whether they
be Elevens... or Britannians!
The Japan Liberation
Front cowardly took
innocent Britannian
civilians hostage
and then mercilessly
executed them.
It was a wanton and
meaningless act.
Therefore, they
have been punished.
[TOHDOH]
Uh?
You heard me right!
I said let it run!
Liable?!
I'll be the one
responsible for this!
[ZERO] Just as former
viceroy Clovis was punished
for ordering the slaughter of
countless unarmed Elevens.
We could not stand by and allow
such cruelty to be carried out.
And so, we made him
pay for his actions.
I will not repudiate battle
on a fair and level field.
But neither will I tolerate a
one-sided massacre of the weak
by the strong!
The only ones who should kill...
...are those of us who are
prepared to be killed!
Wherever oppressors abuse
their power by attacking
those who are powerless,
we shall appear again!
No matter how mighty...
how formidable our foe may be!
[KALLEN]
Knights... for justice?
[ZERO] Those of you
with power... fear us!
Those of you without
it... rally behind us!
We, the Black Knights,
shall be the ones who stand
in judgment of this world!
[LELOUCH]
I was lucky.
Heaven must truly be on my side.
I never expected that
Cornelia's one weakness
was among the hostages.
A weakness named Euphemia.
From now on, the Black Knights
shall become my counterattack.
Against the world in
which I was trapped.
And against my own
undecided heart.