[RETAINER] Your Majesty,
the remains have arrived.
I was just conversing
with Clovis, actually.
[RETAINER]
Huh?
The project must proceed.
Without a moment's delay.
[STUDENT D] What's an
Eleven doing here?!
[PONY TAIL GIRL]
He was a suspect
in Prince Clovis's murder!
[PIG TAILS GIRL] But the teacher
said the charges were dropped.
[STUDENT D]
He was suspicious enough
to arrest though, right?
You don't really think
he's a terrorist, do you?
[KALLEN]
Um?
Of course he isn't.
The school board would
know something like that.
An Eleven here at school?
He is an honorary Britannian.
I know but still, all the same.
Well, he doesn't look
all that scary to me.
Why don't we just talk
to him, I'm sure he's--
Hey.
The guy just got here,
give him some space.
Seven years since we used
this signal. Long time, huh?
Meeting on the roof
like the old days.
[LELOUCH]
Yeah.
I'm glad you're okay.
I've been worried.
Alive and kicking,
thanks to you.
You almost died...
trying to protect me...
I was just returning the favor.
From seven years ago.
What about the girl?
You know, from the capsule?
I don't really know, we got
seperated during the fray.
But you would know more
about her than I do, right?
No. The only ones
who knew anything
were the inner circle
of the Royal Guard.
I see.
[SUZAKU] And your name,
do I still call you Lelouch?
[LELOUCH] The records count
my old identity among the dead.
I go by the name
Lelouch Lamperouge now.
[SUZAKU]
Oh.
[LELOUCH]
And you?
What happened at
your court martial?
And why did you
enroll at this school?
I'm as surprised as you are.
What're the odds that we'd
end up at the same school?
Truth is...
...someone arranged for me to
receive a proper investigation.
And that person said that a
17-year-old should be in school.
[EUPHEMIA] Were all of
these painted by Clovis?
[BUTLER]
Yes.
Such gentle colors...
Very much akin to my brother.
[OFFICER A] We've successfully
identified the guerillas.
[DALTON]
That's good.
Now all we need
is their hideout.
Get that intel to the viceroy!
[OFFICER B]
Yes, my lord!
What the--?!
Is that Cornelia?!
Relics of a forgotten age.
[CORNELIA]
Darlton! In here, correct?
[DALTON] Yes, m'lady.
Shall we accompany you?
[CORNELIA] Not for this
level of resistance.
[DALTON]
Understood.
[CORNELIA] Surrender at once,
you feeble-minded Elevens!
[TERRORISTS]
Down with Britannia!
[CORNELIA]
Doesn't seem Zero is here.
No point in going after them
one at a time, I suppose.
Vermin.
Rot like the filth that you are!
Hi, Lelouch. I've returned home.
Hi, there. Welcome
back. Miss Sayoko.
I've got a special
present for you today.
[NUNNALLY]
Really? What could it be?
[SAYAKO]
Huh?
[gasps]
[NUNNALLY]
This hand.
Thank heaven.
I knew it. I just knew
you'd be all right!
It's been a long time, Nunnally.
[NUNNALLY] So tell me, you will
stay the night, won't you?
Suzaku's enrolled as a student
at Ashford Academy now.
So you can see him
anytime you want.
Is that true?!
[SUZAKU] Well, I still
have military duties,
so I can't be here every day.
Oh, you're... you're
still in the military?
Don't worry.
I've been re-assigned
to the engineering corp.
It's a lot less dangerous.
Oh, cool. Engineering, huh?
Oh! Lemme help you!
You just sit down.
Unlike seven years ago,
we get to be your host now.
[SUZAKU]
Uh.
It's funny, you're a lot more
mellow than you used to be.
And you're a bit more rough.
[LELOUCH]
Ha, I suppose.
Hm?
I told you to stay in my room.
That boy out there.
He's the Britannian soldier
from Shinjuku, isn't he?
Is that wise?
Don't worry, it's fine. He's...
[C.C.]
Hm?
He's a friend... from the past.
[GUILFORD]
You're getting out, Jeremiah.
Lord Guilford!
You see I'm innocent,
don't you?!
Well it seems in the eyes of
the court you are anyway.
Orange boy.
Whatever the truth
is, Zero got away.
And you purebloods
let it happen.
You've been demoted
three ranks for failure.
You have two options
to choose from.
Starting over as a pilot,
or cultivating an orange farm.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
You should come by again.
Nunnally would enjoy it.
[SUZAKU]
Sure. But...
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
Lelouch, I...
I don't think we should be
seen together at school.
What do you mean?
Think. How would you explain it?
Being friends with an
honorary Britannian?
We have to guard your secret.
No one can know you're royalty.
[LELOUCH]
Uh.
And the same goes for Nunnally.
I don't wanna cause
you any trouble--
Doing it again, huh?
Everyone's needs but your own!
[SUZAKU]
Again?
Forget it...
[SUZAKU]
Uh...
Thanks for having me.
It was a lotta fun.
I'll, uh... see you later.
Right.
I'm so glad, ya know?
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
I never thought we'd
get another chance...
...to talk like this.
[STUDENTS chattering]
So, what's the deal?
Something happen to you
yesterday, or what?
Ya didn't even show up
for the council meeting.
You know, I kinda
tanked that history exam.
[RIVALZ]
Please, I don't buy that.
The way you study? I--
[STUDENT A]
Stop it, you guys.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[OHGI]
It hasn't made the news yet,
but the "Blood of
the Samurai" faction
was wiped out by Cornelia.
They were the largest group
we had in Central Japan.
Look, Zero, it won't be long
till she comes after us.
Just keep your head.
Our chance will come.
[OHGI]
But--!
Sit tight, I'll
contact you later.
[LELOUCH] He's getting
too overly familiar...
Maybe I'd better
cut my ties with them.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[NUNNALLY]
Nina?
[gasps]
[NINA]
I'm sorry, am I too loud?
Not at all. Why are you
here? What about class?
Oh...
[NUNNALLY]
Something wrong?
Well, it's... I dunno...
a little scary.
[NUNNALLY]
Scary?
We have a transfer
student in our class now.
It's that boy who was accused
of murdering Prince Clovis.
He's an Eleven.
[gasps]
[DELIVERY BOY]
Oh.
Thanks for all the
repeat business.
Although the name on the account
we debit has a guy's name on it,
is that okay?
[C.C.]
Huh?
Trying to you hide
your mask, huh?
Unlike my Geass, the mask is
a physical piece of evidence.
[knocking]
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
All right, Lelouch. The tea
is ready when you are.
That smell. Hey, did you
ordered pizza again?
I'm racking up reward points.
I'll be right down, okay?
[NUNNALLY]
Lelouch.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[NUNNALLY] Maybe you should
cut down on the pizza.
You don't want a blubbery belly.
Just don't touch
or rub it, okay?
[NUNNALLY]
Ooh, scary!
[LELOUCH chuckles]
[CAT yowls]
[C.C.]
Hm?
What the heck?
[LELOUCH] Yeah... I was
wondering if that was going on.
They're just being
cruel to Suzaku.
No. It's just...
These things take time.
People will come around.
Isn't there anything
you can do though?
I mean, he is your friend.
[CAT meows]
[yelps]
[NUNNALLY]
Huh?
[LELOUCH]
Hey! Give that back!
Uh... Lelouch?
[CAT meowing]
[LELOUCH]
A cat...
A... stupid, little cat!
You've gotta be kidding me!
There's no way I'm getting
exposed by a lousy feline!
[C.C.]
Huh?
That wasn't my fault... was it?
I didn't touch or rub anything.
Hmm.
[NUNNALLY] Yeah, that's right.
I think a cat ran off
with something pretty
important to him.
[MILLY]
Important?
I'm not sure what exactly,
but I'm positive it was
something of value to him.
Because... I've never heard
my brother sound like that!
He was completely hysterical!
That's weird.
What could be so
important to the guy?
A love letter?
An embarrassing photo?
Poetry he wrote?
Poetry?
[RIVALZ, MILLY chuckle]
Leave it to us! We'll get
our hands on this thing
before Lelouch has
a chance to blink!
Just you wait!
[LELOUCH] If I had those
terrorists with me,
we could encircle
the enemy! Maybe Kallen?
No... She's suspicious
of me as it is!
Get it together.
[BLONDE STUDENT] So anyway,
I told him to buzz off, ya know?
[BRUNETTE STUDENT]
Totally. And then?
[BLONDE STUDENT]
C'mon, you can guess, can't you!
[BOTH]
Hm?
What's up with that cat?
Is that the mask Zero
wears? Or am I crazy?
[BRUNETTE STUDENT]
No way. Why would it be here?
You two saw it?!
Forget everything
you've just seen!
[GIRLS]
Sure, no problem at all.
[LELOUCH]
Good.
[MILLY] This is Milly Ashford,
your student council president.
Cat hunt, everybody!
[SUZAKU]
Cat hunt?
There's a cat loose on campus
that needs to be rounded up!
Put everything on hold people.
Participating clubs'll
get budget priority!
And whoever catches
our feline friend
will get an extra special prize!
A big 'ole kiss from one of
the members of the council!
--[SHIRLEY screaming]
--[MILLY laughing]
Members of-- Wait, like me?!?!
[BOYS]
Exactly!
[KALLEN gasps]
You've been hangin' the
student council haven't ya!
Wouldn't mind a
taste 'a those lips!
It's not gonna be like some
lame peck on the cheek though,
is it?!
A kiss on the cheek
would be fine with me!
Wait, we can choose
where she plants it?!
[ALL]
Whoa. Yeah.
[BOYS]
All right!
[BOYS yelling]
There's no way that's how
I'm gonna get my first kiss!
What? From a member
of the student council?
Does that include Lelouch?
Actually, I would
prefer Milly.
[REDHEAD STUDENT]
Ugh.
Could you get back
in the closet please?
[FOOTBALL TEAM]
Hut-hut-hut!
[EQUESTRIAN] We have
the advantage in mobility!
[GARDENER A]
Hurry, look for catnip!
[GARDENER B]
Science will prevail!
[MILLY]
And when you do catch that cat,
bring what it's carrying to me!
To me! To meeee!
[MILLY laughs, coughs]
Milly! Stay out
of this, will ya!
Offering people up as prizes.
That's why I hate Britannians.
[FEM STUDENT G]
I know, crazy, right?
[FEM STUDENT F]
Yeah, I can hardly believe it.
[FEM STUDENT G] I was, like,
floored when I heard it.
[FEM STUDENT F]
All I can say is sign me up!
Dammit! Why do I have to pretend
like I'm sick and feeble?
Jeez, I'm sorry about that--
Shirley, why are you
dressed like that?!
I didn't have time to change!
They're gonna make us kiss
somebody. We've gotta hurry!
I'm with you!
[NINA] Nunnally, is there
anything about this cat
that's special?
[NUNNALLY]
Hm...
I think that its
leg must be hurt
because it's footsteps
sounded off to me.
And uh... Oh!
I almost forgot!
It meowed like this...
Meooowwww!
[STUDENTS]
Meooowwwwwwwwww!
This school seems
so laid back.
In spite of the fact
that they're in mourning.
You suppose Sukzaku will
be all right in here?
[LLOYD] Never mind that.
The university here...
[CECILE] Don't worry, I've
made arrangements with them.
[LLOYD]
Hmm...
They still didn't have to kick
poor Lancelot out though.
[CECILE]
I know.
Even if they did say Elevens
aren't acceptable.
'Kay! Let's go!
What happens if a member of the
student council catches the cat?
We don't get a prize do we?
Do we get a kiss? But of course.
Is that so?
Well, what are we
waitin' around for then?
This is my day t'shine...
[TEACHER]
Hey! No speeding on campus!
[CAT meows, hisses]
Okay, we do this right
and our lips will be safe.
Shirley, you cover the rear.
Wait a sec!
What's the matter?
Who would you wanna
get a kiss from?
Is there anybody in particular?
Huh?
It wouldn't be
Lelou, would it?
Just what would make
you think that?
Oh, well... I guess...
it's just...
[SUZAKU]
Hey, that's...
Suzaku?
Lelouch?! You're
looking for the cat too?
[CAT meowing]
[SUZAKU]
Up there...
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku, wait!
Don't go up there!
But the student council
president said to catch it!
[LELOUCH] Don't worry
about it, I'll get the cat!
[SUZAKU] I was always
more agile than you!
Remember when that
little bird got loose?
[LELOUCH]
Quit talkin' ancient history!
[SUZAKU]
It was only seven years ago!
[LELOUCH]
Oh, for Pete's sake.
He always was an exercise nut...
So someone's got
it cornered, huh?!
Who's the lucky winner?!
Up there!
[SHIRLEY]
Suzaku?
Easy now. You don't
have to be scared.
Suzaku! Come back!
It's all right.
Leave this to me.
[LELOUCH]
That's funny.
He never went along with
the crowd like this.
[yelps]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
Lelouch!
[SUZAKU]
Are you... okay?
[LELOUCH]
Y-Yeah...
Is it possible...
those two are?
[sighs]
Pretty calm for someone
on the verge of death.
Yeah, right. I was
just limp with fear.
[MILLY]
Huh?
Hey, what's going on?
That transfer student
just saved Lelouch
from a really close call.
[NUNNALLY]
Uh.
[SUZAKU] I think it's the
same cat from the other day.
[CAT hisses]
[ALL gasp]
[RIVALZ]
Huh.
You saved him! Thank you
so much, Suzaku!
Yeah, way to go there, new guy!
That cat was carrying
something, wasn't it?
Yeah, there was
something on its head,
but I never really got
a good look at it.
Guess it slipped off
when I wasn't looking.
So where is Lelou?
He said he forgot something.
Told me to go ahead.
That's it! The embarrassing
secret that he's hiding!
[SHIRLEY]
Hm?
[LELOUCH]
So that's it, Madame President?
[ALL]
Hm?
Aww. After all this time, I
thought I had some dirt on you.
Yeah, he almost lost
his cool for once.
So, uh, do you two
know each other, then?
[BOTH gasp]
Yeah, but, he's an Eleven.
No, I just...
[LELOUCH]
He's my friend.
Madame President,
would you permit him as a
member of the student council?
[MILLY, SHIRLEY, RIVALZ]
Huh...?
The rules are clear.
All students are
required to join a club.
Although...
Well, you are the
vice president.
I s'pose I can't refuse.
[SHIRLEY chuckles]
Well then, I'd say
that's the end of that.
Now c'mere you two,
lend me an ear.
Nunnally?
There you go, the reward
Miss Milly promised.
Since you both caught the cat,
you'll just have
to settle for me.
Almost a real council member!
All right then!
Let's celebrate the
catching of the cat!
Everything's on the
new guy, naturally!
Oh, back off!
Hi there, I'm Shirley!
Pleasure to meet 'cha!
[RIVALZ]
Oh, right, I'm Rivalz!
[MILLY] Milly Ashford.
Student council president.
[SUZAKU]
The pleasure is mine.
[RETAINER]
And now, his royal majesty,
the 98th emperor of the
Holy Britannian Empire!
All men.. are not
created equal...
Some are born swifter of foot.
Some with greater beauty.
Some are born into poverty.
And others born sick and feeble.
Both in birth and in upbringing.
In sheer scope of ability, every
human is inheritantly different.
Yes,
that is why people discriminate
against one another.
Which is why there is
struggle, competition,
and the unfaltering
march of progress.
Inequality...
...is not wrong. Equality is.
What of the EU, which
made equality a right?
Rabble politics by
a popularity contest!
The Chinese Federation with its
equal distribution of wealth?
A nation of lazy dullards...
But not our beloved Britannia.
We fight. We compete.
Evolution is continuous.
Evolution. Such a
pretty little word.
Britannia alone moves forward,
advancing steadily
into the future.
Even the death of my son Clovis,
demonstrates Britannia's
unswerving commitment
to progress.
We will fight on!
We shall struggle, compete,
plunder, and dominate!
And in the end, the
future shall be ours.
All hail Britannia.
[ALL]
All hail Britannia!
[C.C.] So... This is
Lelouch's enemy. Well.
[LELOUCH] The word "hatred"
is not strong enough...
If my father is the
embodiment of Brittannia,
he must be detroyed!
And if Cornelia gets in my way,
she'll suffer the same fate!
You may not know it yet,
but I have power!
So long as I possess Geass,
I can go this alone.