Long live the Black Knights!
Hip, hip, hooray!
[CROWD cheering]
[KALLEN] What happened
to that Knightmare?
The one that saved Zero?
It escaped using a
route Xing-ke gave us.
[LELOUCH]
Xing-ke?
The Chinese Federation
guy I mentioned.
[LELOUCH]
I see.
Then I'll be sure to make
use of that route, as well.
So, was that pilot the same
one from Babel Tower?
[LELOUCH] Because of
what happened to Urabe,
I won't tell you his name.
Simply think of him as a
person who supports our cause.
You didn't use your
Geass on him, did you?
[LELOUCH] As it turned out,
I didn't need to.
Anyway, C.C., about
the Emperor and--
Now wait a minute!
You'll keep the pilot
a secret from me?!
So what?
There are times when
I like to keep secrets, too.
Are you speaking as Zero,
or Lelouch right now?
It's not as if
everyone knows about
our relationship, do they?
Stop saying weird stuff
like that, all right?!
And your true identity?
Kallen and I are the only
ones among the group
who know who you really are.
That's secret, too.
[KALLEN] Lelouch, do you still
want me to be the captain
of Zero's personal force,
as I have been?
[LELOUCH]
I do.
[KALLEN]
Understood.
I'll consider that
roger and out!
I'm counting on you, now.
[door hisses]
We'll talk about Geass later.
There are more pressing matters.
Very well. I catch your drift.
Here it is! Man,
I've missed my old uniform!
Rock n' roll...!
[BLACK KNIGHT A] I can't believe
they had all this ready for us!
[BLACK KNIGHT B]
They say Captain Kouzuki
and Urabe arranged it.
[BLACK KNIGHT C]
Oh man...
Oh, I see. And you
say Urabe died well?
Yes.
You should just
confess already.
W-What do you
mean by "confess?"
[BLACK KNIGHT C]
It's Zero!
[BLACK KNIGHTS chatter]
Hold it! Hold it!
While we appreciate
your rescuing us, Zero,
we wouldn't have been
captured in the first place
if you hadn't betrayed
us the way you did!
Don't you owe us an explanation?
[KALLEN gasps]
What happened?
We deserve to know!
[ZERO] Everything is for
victory over Britannia.
Okay... Go on.
[ZERO]
That's all.
[BLACK KNIGHTS]
Huh?!
Nothing more to say?
No apologies? No excuses?
[TOHDOH]
Stop it!
Zero.
Were your actions intended to
give us a chance of winning?
[ZERO] I'm always focused
on getting results.
I understand.
[CHIBA gasps]
At times, our operations
must be kept secret.
Right now, we need
to rely on his power!
I can think of no
one more capable
than Zero to be our leader!
I agree! We should
all trust Zero!
But Zero treated you as if you
were nothing more than a pawn.
Who other than Zero could
have pulled this off?!
Even the Chinese Federation
isn't strong enough
to wage war on Britannia!
And the E.U. continues to lose
to Prince Schneizel, doesn't it?
We're the last hope
out of all the Areas
that Britannia
has colonized.
Zero is the only one who
can lead us to victory
in our war of independence!
Ohgi's right!
Zero! Zero! Zero! Zero!
[BLACK KNIGHTS]
Zerp! Zero! Zero! Zero...
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Hello, everyone.
My name is Suzaku Kururugi,
and I'll be returning to
classes here at Ashford
Academy starting today.
I look forward to
studying here.
[MALE STUDENT 1]
Suzaku Kururugi?!
[MALE STUDENT 2]
The guy who caught Zero?!
[MALE STUDENT 3] The White Death
is coming to school here?!
[FEMALE STUDENT 1]
He's the Knight of Seven.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
But, he's an Eleven.
[FEM STUDENT 1]
Doesn't matter.
He's the emperor's
immediate subord--
[VILLETTA]
Okay, quiet down!
Sir Kururugi has been
reassigned to Area 11,
and that's why he's coming
back to school here.
Why don't you take the desk
next to Lelouch for now.
[SUZAKU]
Yes, ma'am.
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku... You...
You were my first real friend.
[SUZAKU]
But... the war tore us apart.
[LELOUCH]
The Second Pacific War.
The conflict in which Britannia
took control of Japan.
[SUZAKU]
After it's defeat,
Japan became an Area
colony of Britannian.
[LELOUCH] I, who was
abandoned by my homeland...
[SUZAKU] I, who was forced
to abandon my homeland...
[LELOUCH] When reunited, we were
at once enemies and allies.
[SUZAKU]
Although I was Japanese,
I was also a Britannian soldier.
[LELOUCH]
I was Zero.
We both hid our true identities.
[SUZAKU]
We fought each other.
[LELOUCH]
However, those are memories
of what really happened.
[SUZAKU] The emperor
rewrote three things
in Lelouch's memory.
[LELOUCH]
Nunnally...
[SUZAKU]
Anything about Zero...
[LELOUCH]
And that I...
...was a prince of the
royal family of Britannia.
[LELOUCH, SUZAKU]
And so, the two of us now...
Hey, welcome back.
It's been some time.
I missed everyone a lot.
Suzaku, it feels like forever!
You've really come up
in the world, haven't you!
Suzaku's back?! Where is he?!
Madame President!
Class is in progress. You mind?
[MILLY] Oh, what's
with you, Lelouch?
[LELOUCH]
You screwed up, Suzaku.
When you heard the name Lelouch,
you just walked
right to my side.
In other words, you acted
as if you knew me.
Now, to make sure Rolo
doesn't do anything stupid.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[gasps]
[SHIRLEY] And so everybody
up and left, except us.
They all went back home.
Even the teachers!
[SUZAKU]
Back to the homeland?
[LELOUCH]
Yeah.
And that's the reason
why we're the only ones
here at the school who
know you. Right, Rolo?
[ROLO]
R-Right.
That explains why I don't
recognize any one here.
Hey, you saw
Zero's face, didn't you?
So what did he look like?
Is he really a girl?
It's really
Prince Clovis, right?
Or a prince from
another country?
Uhh...well, um...
Can't you share that with us?
No, it's a military secret.
--I'm sorry-- Ah!
--[ARTHUR growls]
Arthur!
Ah! You brought him with you?
[LELOUCH]
Well, Suzaku,
you really have a thing
for cats, don't you?
[VILLETTA]
Did anything leap out at you
during your contact with him?
[SUZAKU]
No, not especially.
[VILLETTA]
Then we can conclude that
the subject's memories
haven't returned?
Wait just a minute.
Please, I feel we have to
investigate this further.
Do you mean you don't
trust our surveillance?
There's also the matter of C.C.
Continue playing
his little brother
just the way you have been.
All right, my lord.
It seems the student council
is planning to throw
you a welcoming party.
Please reconfirm his state then.
Yes, understood.
[ROLO]
What should I do?
Do I dare trust Lelouch?
Teacher, could you
please overlook
all the campus infractions that
Rolo and I are involved in?
Very well. I can do that.
Just don't wander off
school grounds
so often, you two.
[LELOUCH, ROLO]
Yes, sir.
The only member left
now is Ms. Villetta, right?
[ROLO]
Correct.
But Suzaku Kururugi is here now.
Shall I kill him?
You shouldn't behave like that.
Oh, and something else...
[ROLO]
Yes?
[LELOUCH] Can you quit speaking
to me in such a formal manner?
After all, we are
supposed to be brothers.
[ROLO]
Uh!
[LELOUCH]
Don't worry.
I'll hurry up with my plan
for your sake, as well.
I am going to do it.
Independence for Japan,
will begin with this school.
[EDGAR]
Iwate.
Wakayama.
Tokushima.
[CLAUDIO] There are
reports from Yamaguchi, too.
[scoffs]
Zero makes an appearance again,
and now we get this!
[CLAUDIO] It may be an effect
of Lord Guilford's absence, too.
[EDGAR] If this keeps up,
our Sakuradite supply
--will also be--
--[booming]
[SOLDIER]
Emergency!
Unknown M.R.F.
within the perimeter!
What is it?!
No way! This government
bureau controls all of Area 11!
[GINO laughs] Getting in here
couldn't have been easier!
These guys are almost
annoyingly sloppy!
Is this the best line of defense
that Area 11's got to offer?
[GINO] Uh-huh. Perhaps I
was being a bit hasty.
[yells]
Oh?
I don't know who you are,
but this ends right here!
Pitiful. That armament shows
you care more about
protecting the building.
Oh well, too bad.
What?!
That Knightmare!
Could it be the one?!
I see, that's what
we're dealing with.
The variable
Knightmare Frame, Tristan.
Which makes you
Lord Gino Weinberg,
the Knight of Three.
Am I correct?
You are. I'm putting
you guys to the test.
Alright! Try and stop me!
[CLAUDIO] Very well.
We accept your challenge!!
We can't allow this insult
to us go unanswered!
Don't hold back.
Gimme your best shot.
[EDGAR]
As you wish!
[GINO]
Thank you!
[CLAUDIO]
Why, you...!
Stop it!
That's enough!
The battle's been decided!
Then, Sir Kururugi,
is that the final decision
of the Knight of Seven?
[SUZAKU]
It is.
[grunts]
Hey, Suzaku!
[SUZAKU]
Gino, I thought I asked you
to bring Lancelot here for me.
[GINO] Yeah, but Earl Asplund
is coming with it next week.
And not to change the subject,
but what's with that outfit?
I came straight here
from school. It's required.
Very fashionable!
[SUZAKU grunts]
Gino, I know you're from
a great, noble family,
but can't you act more normal?
By the way,
you're amazingly heavy.
[ANYA]
Is it over?
[SUZAKU] The Mordred?
Anya came along, too?
Is it over?
[GINO]
Yup. Suzaku made me end it.
Ohh...
[ANYA]
How dull.
[SUZAKU] We should have
more than enough firepower
assembled by now.
Lelouch, three days from now,
at the welcome party,
everything will be made clear.
Apologies for the delay!
We are now officially kicking
off the welcome party
for the Knight of Seven!
Give the word, guest of honor.
Yeah, um... I don't
suppose I can refuse?
Sorry, nope! It's a
presidential order!
Just accept it. She sets
the rules in this school.
[SUZAKU]
Hmph. All right, guys.
I'll get ready, then.
[deep breath]
[SUZAKU]
Meow!
[FESTIVAL CROWD chatters]
[cheering]
[screams]
[EQUESTRIAN STUDENT] This way
to the horseback riding course!
[ROLO] Lelouch, are these things
appropriate for the occasion?
[LELOUCH] That's Milly for ya.
The Prez loves events like this.
She's also overcompensating
for last year.
[ROLO]
Oh?
[ROLO] What should I
do now? I ought to just--
[LELOUCH]
Rolo.
[ROLO]
Huh?
[LELOUCH] I've told you,
that's dangerous.
Here, hold your knife
like this. Got it?
[ROLO]
L-Like this?
Careful of your fingers.
[ROLO]
Mm.
--[ROLO] Lelouch.
--[LELOUCH] Hm?
The truth is... my Geass
does have an Achilles heel.
Wow, would you look at that!
Hey Anya, check it out!
[camera beeping]
Recorded.
You sure love that stuff, huh?
All right, so now what?
There's nothing in
particular to do here.
Shall we take a tour of where
the commoners go to school?
I'm here now.
In the storehouse
under the school.
Okay, so where are those
spare energy fillers?
Hm?
Hey, didn't these
belong to Nina?
[LELOUCH]
All right. Understood.
Go through cell F in Kyushu
and make contact with Diethard.
Yes, that's right.
Have Rakshata come here and...
She wouldn't!
[RIVALZ] Come and watch us make
the world's biggest pizza pie!
Do you have
information about it?
Of course!
Here's a flyer for you!
Come see the world's
biggest pizza!
[LELOUCH] Hey! What do
you think... you're doing?
I'm looking for
something I left behind.
Why are you so obsessed
with this stuff anyway?
Come on!
[C.C.] Acting a little
devilish aren't you?
[LELOUCH]
Shut up, witch!
Don't you understand
your situation?
[C.C.] The emperor is
trying to capture me.
And he's using you as bait.
[LELOUCH]
That's right. Suzaku's here.
As well as another. A woman
I can't use my Geass on.
From pretty girls...
To sexy grownup women!
[SWIM CLUB STUDENTS]
Welcome to the Swim Club Café,
where you get exactly
what you want!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Oh, I'm so glad the coach
agreed to do this for us!
[VILLETTA]
So help me, Shirley,
you'll die a thousand
deaths for this!
If I didn't have to play
teacher for my mission, I'd...!
I used to be a schoolteacher,
so I was feeling
a little nostalgic.
[SUZAKU] They've confirmed
that the Guren Mark-2 is there.
I assume Kallen is in
the consulate building.
--I see. It's hard to judge her.
--[ARTHUR meows]
They call themselves "resistance
fighters," but still...
Nina's doing quite well.
She just presented a thesis
at the Science Academy.
[MILLY]
I wonder if she's planning
to perfect the Ganymede.
[SUZAKU]
Don't know.
Unlike Lloyd and Cecile,
Nina's specialty is--
Uh?
[MILLY] Um, has Earl Asplund
happened to mention me?
[ARTHUR whimpers]
Afraid not.
[MILLY]
Maybe he was overwhelmed?
The wedding was put off because
I had to repeat school.
[SUZAKU]
The thing with him is...
So many things are wrong
with him as a human being,
so--Uh! What the--?
[ARTHUR meowing]
[SUZAKU]
Arthur! That was Euphie's!
Suzaku!
You're the guest of honor!
You have to wait here!
You can't run off like that!
[GINO]
What have we here?
They're using a Knightmare
to create a giant pizza?!
[LELOUCH] So, the person who
gave the emperor his Geass
is the same person
who told Suzaku?
[C.C.]
That's right.
But you shouldn't delve
into it any further.
[LELOUCH] I'm already
involved in this.
V.V.
V.V.?
Did he give Suzaku
a Geass power?
[C.C.] No, it doesn't
appear that he did.
Aanyway, about Villetta--
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu!
[C.C.]
Uh?
--What's up, Shirley?
--[C.C. grunts]
[SHIRLEY]
Hm? Oh, there you are.
[LELOUCH]
Do you need something?
[SHIRLEY]
Well, I have a little problem
that I hope you
can help me with.
Ms. Villetta seems
to be avoiding me,
so I was thinking you should...
Huh? You're alone?
[LELOUCH]
Yeah.
I could've sworn you were
talking to someone just now.
Nope. We're the only ones here,
just the two of us.
[C.C. grunts]
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[SHIRLEY] Just the two of us?
What awful timing,
but this might be my best
chance to tell him how I feel.
Listen, um, Lulu.
Would you go out--
[yelps]
[LELOUCH] Sorry, but I
couldn't quite catch that.
Hey! What's the big idea?!
[LELOUCH]
What are you doing?!
If someone spots you, as well--
Don't worry! I'm came here
to take Pizza Girl back!
[LELOUCH] Fine. She's in
with the tomatoes.
Take the whole container,
then have Tohdoh or
Ohgi command the--
[LELOUCH groans]
[LELOUCH, SHIRLEY yelp]
Who's in there being so rude!
[LELOUCH groans]
How undignified!
[SHIRLEY] Will you quit standing
there and say something!
[KALLEN] If I say something,
she'll find out who I am!
[SHIRLEY]
Ugh! Hey, wait!
Shirley! Be careful with that!
--Hey, Lelouch!
--[LELOUCH] Huh?
Say, have you seen Arthur?!
He grabbed a valuable
quill pen from me, and--
[banging]
[LELOUCH]
Uh!
[C.C. grunts]
[SUZAKU] Oh no, is he
inside this thing?!
[LELOUCH]
No! Cats and tomatoes don't mix!
[gasps]
[KALLEN gasps]
[GINO] You're supposed
to start with this, right?
[SUZAKU]
It can't be... Gino?!
Yeah! This commoner
school is really a blast!
Hey! Wait!
[SHIRLEY grunts]
Hey!
[ARTHUR]
Hm?
[ARTHUR yelps]
[KALLEN, SHIRLEY grunting]
Was that Arthur?
[MILLY sighs] Now we'll
have to change the schedule.
[RIVALZ] It looks
like it's coming out
onto the parade route now!
They'll be marched around
the school building first,
then make their way down here!
Even though it's a
vintage Knightmare,
it's handling well.
Okay, the route's all set, so...
Shake time!
[C.C. grunting]
[LELOUCH]
What a mess!
He's taking her
straight to the stage!
Let me at least
see who you are!
[SUZAKU grunts]
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH panting] I'm not
cut out for this sort of thing.
[MILLY]
Release the hounds!
[LELOUCH growls]
[FESTIVAL CROWD chatters]
[RIVALZ]
Over there!
The Knight of Seven,
Suzaku Kururugi!
He's arrived, along with our
Andes-grown Ultimate Tomatoes!
Suzaku, come on over!
You're the one we've
been waiting for!
[RIVALZ]
Uh. Except that...
There's a different
person piloting!
[FESTIVAL CROWD gasps]
Ah! Whoa!
[C.C. grunts]
Team Leader 1! Turn around,
and look up at me!
Yes, what is it, Vice President?
Employ system pattern rouge!
Now going to system
pattern rouge.
Release fire-extinguishing gas.
Initiating.
[ALL gasping, coughing]
[SHIRLEY yelps]
[GINO laughing]
What's the matter?
Is it really that
much of a surprise?
What the hell's
going on here?! Ugh!
Sorry. Are you okay?
Uh, oh no,
it was my fault.
Ah!
[KALLEN]
That was...
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
[camera beeping]
Recorded. Thank you, Miss.
No problem. You're welcome.
[SUZAKU]
Oh, Arthur.
[MILLY]
Well, sometimes you just get
these little filler
incidents in life.
And that's fine!
[LELOUCH]
So then?
The person who saw you
was from the Swim Club?
[KALLEN] I think it may
have been the teacher.
[LELOUCH]
Villetta?!
[KALLEN]
I didn't get her name.
But the weird thing is that
I think I remember seeing her
at the festival
last year with Ohgi.
Ohgi and Villetta?
[KALLEN] Minami said that Ohgi
might have had a collaborator
who reported directly to him.
Ohgi kept a secret from me?
[C.C.] When it comes
to these sorts of things,
you're really very thick.
The truth is...
That's it, Rolo?
You've turned traitor?
[LELOUCH]
Villetta Nu.
The woman who was
awarded the rank of baron
for ascertaining
Zero's real identity.
But unknown to most,
you're connected to
the Black Knights.
Not true! I never betrayed--
Kaname Ohgi.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
If word of your relationship
with him ever got out,
you'd have to
relinquish that title
you worked so
hard to earn.
Why not be reborn
as someone new?
Oh, yes.
Shirley gave me
this to give to you,
so the timing works out nicely.
Happy birthday, Coach Villetta.
[LELOUCH]
It seems I owe you another debt.
[XING-KE] I simply used
my diplomatic immunity.
Besides, I'd like to repay my
debt to you as quick as I can.
[LELOUCH] Then, may I
ask another favor of you?
I don't like to be in
collusion with you.
[LELOUCH] I'd like to get in
contact with the High Eunuchs.
[XING-KE gasps]
[LELOUCH] The only one
left to defeat is Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch?
[LELOUCH]
Mm?
Shouldn't the guest of
honor be at the main stage?
[SUZAKU]
Hm? No.
Everyone seems to be having
a fine time without me.
Besides, I want to discuss
something with you.
[LELOUCH]
What is it?
Well you see...
I'm aspiring to become
the Knight of One.
[LELOUCH]
Whoa!
That's the greatest knight
in the entire empire--
The Knight of One is
bestowed the privilege
of choosing one of the
Britannian Areas for his own.
I intend to have Japan.
I'll take this area for myself.
[SUZAKU] Lelouch, I've lost
too much; Precious friends
and a woman who no
one can ever replace.
By acquiring power,
I will never again lose
anyone else I care about.
And then, the Japanese people
won't need Zero any more.
[LELOUCH]
Hm? Indirect rule, huh?
You wanna make
it a protectorate?
You can ask this person.
--They'll know.
--[phone beeps]
Huh?
[SUZAKU] The new viceroy
who's coming to take charge
of Area 11 next week.
You think a student should
speak to the viceroy?
[SUZAKU]
It's Kururugi.
Yes. He's standing right
here in front of me.
Yes.
What do I say?
How awkward.
This is such an
important person.
[NUNNALLY]
Hello? Big Brother?
[LELOUCH gasps]
Lelouch, is that you?!
It's me! Nunnally!
Can you hear me?
I'm coming there
to be the viceroy!
Um, is there
something wrong?
Lelouch, it's Nunnally.
Your sister.
[LELOUCH]
At this very moment,
Nunnally is on the
other end of the phone.
Does she know that
I'm Zero? No, I doubt it.
Then this must be a trick Suzaku
is perpetrating against me.
Because if I respond
to my little sister,
he'll know that my
memories have returned.
He's using Nunnally to trap me!
Nunnally! Suzaku!
No matter how he wears
the face of a friend,
his true face is that of
the fiend who sold me
to the emperor!
There mere thought
that he's been at
my sister's side!