[SUZAKU] Two thousand ten
of the imperial calendar.
The Holy Britannian Empire
invaded Japan to gain control
of its underground
Sakuradite resources.
My father Genbu called
for do-or-die resistance.
To stop him, I...
It was childish.
A tragically childish,
impulsive act.
I thought to myself
"This will stop the war."
I thought that there would be
no more needless bloodshed.
But I was wrong.
The fighting didn't stop.
All I wanted was to keep people
from killing each other.
[SUZAKU]
No! It was Geass!
The power that can
twist a man's will!
[SUZAKU]
In the end, it's the same.
I...! Hm?
[NINA] I didn't know.
I didn't understand that...
That it would be this horrible.
That so many people would...
That I... That it would be a--
Massacre.
[NINA]
Uh!
[SUZAKU]
It's a big hit, Nina.
The F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead
has proven itself.
Britannia can't lose now.
[LELOUCH] The Emperor
was headed for Area 11,
but he never showed up in
the Tokyo Settlement...
Which means he had
another objective.
His path could have taken
him to Shikine Island. No!
The ruins on Kamine Island?!
[PRIEST A] According to the
materials left behind by
Director V.V. and our brethren,
this location is optimal.
[PRIEST B]
It will synchronize
with ancient ruins
throughout the world.
[PRIEST C] With this action, we
can make the Sword of Akasha
manageable once again.
[EMPEROR] Heh. I never
imagined I would use such
an ancient device.
It's quite astounding.
[ANYA whimpering]
[ANYA]
So, you're ready to begin then.
[DIETHARD] What's the
Shinkiroh's location?!
[RADIO GUY]
Sir, we don't know yet.
[DIETHARD] Tsk! We have the
Britannians assisting us now!
As soon as you find it, alert
all forces and destroy it!
[RADIO GUY]
Yes, sir!
Master is in danger. Uh!
[ANYA] It's been ages since we
were face to face like this!
It's me!
[C.C.]
Uh!
C.C., don't tell me
you've actually--
I'm so sorry!
[ANYA]
What are you doing,
closing yourself up in
here again like this?
C.C.? C.C.!
[C.C.]
Hm?
Who are you?
[ANYA]
It's me. See?
It's you! So, you've chased
me all the way in here, now?
Are you that worried
about Lelouch, Marianne?
Oh, come on!
Do you really think
I'm such an ideal mother that
that's all I think about?
Then why did you
come here for me?
[MARIANNE]
Because so much has changed;
I need to know if
you're still on my side.
[C.C.]
Huh?
C.C., why did you seal
off your own Code
just when you had
what you wanted?
Charles was ready to grant your
greatest wish: the wish to die.
But you stopped him.
[C.C.]
Even I don't know why I did it.
Actually, I'm a little
shocked that I did.
[MARIANNE laughs]
Then you have to find the
answer, in the real world.
[C.C.]
Hm...
I've made up my mind, and
that's all there is to it.
[C.C.]
How typical of you.
Why is that?
The one who always comes in
and messes around with my life.
[MARIANNE, ANYA] Because I
appreciate what you did.
At least as far as giving
me my Geass Power.
[C.C.] And you never
fulfilled your contract.
If that's what you think,
will you come with me now?
Yes, but wait a minute.
There's something I
can't leave behind.
[ANYA]
Hm?
[CORNELIA] Was there any
chance to tell Anya to stay?
[VILLETTA gasps]
[CORNELIA] We'll need someone
here to take custody of Zero.
So, what do you plan
to do, Villetta?
Stay with the Black Knights?
Uh.
[CORNELIA] Neither my brother
nor myself plan to punish you.
After all, now that things have
moved forward to the next level,
I'd say we have no authority
to act against you.
[VILLETTA]
Well, I...
[exhales] I'm probably the
last person to say this,
but noble rank isn't everything.
[VILLETTA]
Uh...
[DIETHARD]
There's no choice.
We have to announce that
Zero was killed in battle.
[OHGI] Even though we
haven't found Lelouch yet?
[TOHDOH] You want people
to believe he's dead?
Pardon me. I understand
that Zero has betrayed us
and all of that,
but do you plan on telling
everyone about Geass?
We can't, they'd say
we were crazy;
we'd lose all credibility.
There's no way.
And what if the real
Zero appears later?
[DIETHARD] How exactly would he
prove that he's the real Zero?
[OHGI]
Uh?
In the end, the masked
hero is merely a symbol.
He can't re-establish
himself without us.
Oh, really? That's very
good news! Excellent.
[RIVALZ] Yeah! They finally
got the cell phones
working again and we got the
news that everyone is okay!
It was a gigasmic relief.
Ah... Oh, yeah,
your room was destroyed, but
there's space in the clubhouse.
[LELOUCH] I see. Is the student
council room all right?
[RIVALZ] Mm-hm. By the way,
where's Rolo? Is he with you?
Uh, Yeah Listen, Rivalz...
Can you tell the Prez something
for me? Tell her I won't be able
to keep my promise to shoot
off fireworks with everyone.
Huh? What was that
supposed to mean?
Sorry, Rivalz and good luck.
Kallen, take care of C.C...
I have to kill him,
even if I die doing it.
I'm gambling that I can kill
an immortal who never ages
and who is immune to
the power of Geass.
That's the only
chance I have left!
[PRIEST A] Preparations are
complete, Your Majesty.
[EMPEROR]
Very well. Let us begin.
I feel something shaking.
Oh, really?
[PRIEST A] All relic systems
are now synchronized.
[EMPEROR] With this, shall end
the world of the existing God.
Destruction and creation...
Ragnarok has finally begun!
Your Majesty,
Prince Schneizel sent a
report on the conflict in--
[EMPEROR]
Did I not tell you
to leave these mundane
affairs to him?
Mundane affairs?
[EMPEROR] Has the truth finally
begun to dawn on you, Schneizel?
If so, it's too late. This game
called war is already obsolete.
[MILLY]
This is KT Television.
Since our studios were
lost in the blast,
we've set up a temporary
studio at Ashford Academy
to bring you this
emergency news alert.
A short while ago, we
received official word
that Prince Schneizel
has signed a cease fire
with the Black Knights.
In addition, according to an
official announcement, Zero,
leader and CEO of
the Black Knights,
was killed in the final battle.
Zero was wounded in the fight
for the Tokyo Settlement
and subsequently received
medical treatment
aboard the flagship Ikaruga,
but he succumbed to his injuries
before daybreak this morning.
[MAN B]
Master Zero!
--[WOMAN B] No! No!
--[MAN C] It can't be true!
[JEREMIAH] What's the
meaning of this, Ohgi?
Is it true that Zero is dead?!
[OHGI] Yeah. I'm afraid it's
just as the media's reporting.
Could I at least see
his face to confirm it?
[OHGI] Sorry, but we're busy
right now, Jeremiah.
It'll have to wait till later.
[KALLEN]
Are you serious about this?
[OHGI] The Black Knights
don't need Zero anymore!
[KALLEN] We've only gotten
this far because of him!
To just throw him away
like he's disposable...
He's the one who treated us
like we were disposable!
[KALLEN gasps]
[OHGI] He fooled us
from the very beginning!
With that despicable
Geass power!
I called him my friend!
The best friend that I ever had!
I loved that guy more
than my own life!
But then...
We learned the truth.
Think about the Black Rebellion.
He was ready to dispose of Ohgi
then. No. Even before that.
[OHGI]
That's right. People are...
...more than just game pieces!
Their lives matter.
That's why we're fighting!
[OFFICERS grunting]
Lelouch vi Britannia
now commands you!
From this moment forward,
you shall obey my orders!
Damn, she's good.
Lloyd, can you give me an update
on the status of the Lancelot?
You know the status. You saw the
condition of the core luminous.
No, I'm talking about
the Lancelot Albion.
[CECILE]
It's ready to roll out.
Albion? So what's that about?
Oh, I shouldn't have
mentioned that.
It's a custom Knightmare
built for Suzaku.
But in the state
of mind you're in,
I don't want you going near it.
Lloyd, as the Knight of Seven,
I could order you to do it.
[LLOYD]
My unease grows worse and worse.
[CECILE] Suzaku, didn't you say
that you had to be prepared
not to fire the F.L.E.I.J.A.?
[SUZAKU] Miss Cecile, what's
the fundamental purpose
of any weapon?
Sir Kururugi, you want to debate
this like a school boy?
[SUZAKU]
The point is...
[GINO] Drop it, Suzaku.
This isn't like you.
[GINO]
Huh?
Your Highness!
It's all right. You can relax.
[LLOYD]
Princess Cornelia!
It's been far too long,
Your Highness!
Right.
Where is Lord Guilford?
Uh! Well...
Cornelia, I'm afraid Lord
Guilford was caught in the--
[KANON]
He went missing after
he launched the
F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
It was his heroism
that saved all of us.
[CORNELIA]
Guilford?!
[SCHNEIZEL] We may not
know if he's alive or dead,
but he did a great deed.
You should be proud of him. He
served you well as your knight.
What are you saying?!
I'm the one who fired
the F.L.E.I.J.A. warhead.
[CORNELIA, KANON gasp]
[SUZAKU]
That was my deed of honor!
The feat I needed to
become the Knight of One!
[GINO]
Hold on, Suzaku...
Is this manipulation designed to
protect Lord Guilford's legacy?
[CORNELIA]
What are you saying?
[SCHNEIZEL]
I suggest you stop, Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
No. I've been naive up till now.
[LLOYD]
No, you?
[SUZAKU]
Stubbornly maintaining that
the means are more important
than the end result.
I was idealistic and
self-righteous.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Perhaps, but...
In any case, I insist on what
is due me, Your Highness.
Make me the Knight of One.
Huh?
You've crossed the line into
insubordination, Kururugi!
Anyway, only an Emperor has
the power to dub a warrior
the Knight of One.
Which means...
I shall rise to this.
[ALL]
Huh?!
Brother!
If I become the emperor,
it will remove the problem;
it's really as simple as that.
Highness, what you said
just now is close--
Gino.
[GINO]
What are you planning to do?!
Prince Schneizel, can
you please tell us all
what has lead you
to make this decision?
He considers our affairs
"trivial" and " mundane."
[CORNELIA gasps]
[GINO gasps]
[SCHNEIZEL]
That's how His Majesty referred
to our mortal struggle
with the Black Knights.
But...
You've seen it too, Cornelia.
How absorbed Father is with
his dangerous research.
How he abandons the throne.
It's true.
He treats diplomacy and war like
they were meaningless trifles.
A man who's lost interest in
this world who sees his people
locked in a life and
death struggle,
and shrugs in indifference,
such a man has no right to rule!
[KANON] He's finally
made up his mind. But...
Could it be? A coup d'état?!
That's wrong...
[SUZAKU] Your Highness,
as a Knight of the Round,
I can arrange an audience
with the Emperor.
Please give me the order
to assassinate him.
Suzaku!
[SUZAKU] If I'm predestined
to be a killer, then so be it.
Gino, I know what I am and what
I must do. What matters...
are results!
[KAGUYA] Now then, Your Majesty,
as we previously arranged,
I'll conduct negotiations
with Prime Minister
Schneizel in Tokyo.
But, Kaguya. After all,
Zero was your husband.
Losing Master Zero is a
terrible blow it's true...
But we can't dwell on that
when our nations are in danger.
We must turn his death
to our best advantage.
And honestly, I know I
called myself his wife,
but he and I were just...
That is, in the end, we were
married, but, in heart only.
[SUZAKU] His Majesty has
landed on Kamine Island?
[RADIO GUY B]
Yes, my lord,
along with an unknown
group of subjects.
[SUZAKU] Unknown group...
Survivors of the Geass Order?
Are you serious about
sending Suzaku
to assassinate your own father?
Gino, do you want this war to
remain in a stalemate forever?
What do you mean?
The true nature
of people is this:
they want to be controlled.
By their nation, their
religion, their traditions,
and by figures of
grand authority.
Above all, the Emperor of
Britannia must play his part.
[GINO] So now you're the one to
play that part, Your Highness?
The grand authority?
If I am called upon to
do it, then perhaps...
Perhaps? How so?
Did you know that
the word "authority"
actually has another meaning?
[PRIEST A groaning]
Was this treason
Schneizel's idea?
It was my decision.
Majesty, I appreciate
your patronage,
that cannot be questioned.
But, you are guilty
of two crimes!
[EMPEROR]
Oh?
[SUZAKU] First, abandoning your
responsibilities as Emperor.
And second...
...dirtying your hands
with the power of Geass!
Is that a capital crime?
[SUZAKU] Geass takes good
men and bends them to evil.
You knew that.
You could have saved Euphy.
It would have been so easy.
But instead you abandoned her!
[EMPEROR]
So what?
You also drove Lelouch
and Nunnally away;
their despair is in this sword.
Die!
Lord Waldstein! What
are you doing here?
Did you think you were the only
one who knew about Geass?
It takes many forms.
Who could be foolish
enough to relax his guard
with a man who constantly
betrays everyone who trusts him.
Bismarck, I leave this
mundane matter to you.
Yes, Your Majesty, so be it.
Hold on!
[HONG GU] Ohgi? This is Hong Gu.
Requesting landing clearance.
We've brought Her Majesty
and Lady Kaguya with us.
[OHGI]
Uh, right.
Uh. Then I'll contact
Schneizel's staff as well.
[DIETHARD] I thought Ohgi had
finally changed a bit, but no.
Definitely miscast.
His true nature is
to be defensive.
[SUZAKU] No. The Geass command
that compels me to live.
It's screaming at
me to run away!
Is the Knight of One really
that dangerous an opponent?!
I've left my weakness!
[BISMARCK] "Weakness?" Fool,
what you call "weakness"...
[SUZAKU groans]
[BISMARCK] That was the
source of your strength.
Gentleness and compassion
are what drove you!
Take those away and there's
nothing left but violence.
Which means...
[SUZAKU growing]
[BISMARCK] You will die here,
Suzaku Kururugi!
--[explosion]
--[BISMARCK] Huh?!
My name is Lelouch vi Britannia!
I am the eldest son
of Empress Marianne!
The prince who was
abandoned by his empire!
[CHARLY COMMANDER]
We can't contact His Majesty!
If you encounter
anyone suspicious,
don't capture them, kill them!
[CHARLY PILOT]
Yes, my lord!
What are you doing?!
Why are you shooting at-- Ah!
[MONICA] Why are we
attacking our own forces?!
[CHARLY OP A]
We're still confirming,
but we can't contact
gun turret room 3!
[CHARLY OP B] Someone may have
seized the weapons system!
[CHARLY GUARD A]
Respond! Turret room 3!
If you do not respond now,
we will remove you by force!
[CHARLY GUARD B]
Follow us, the royal guard!
We'll eliminate all enemies!
[CHARLY SOLDIER]
Yes, my lord!
Uh!
[CHARLY OP C] The reinforcements
from the Shikine Island base
are attacking us!
[CHARLY OP D] We're getting
reports of our own guards
turning on us as well!
[MONICA]
This is...
A damned rebellion!
[CHARLY OP E] Yes, my lord!
Where is the Emperor?
His Majesty is in the safest
possible place. For now, we...
[SUZAKU]
Lelouch! It's my burden!
[SUZAKU grunting]
Ah!
Who is in command aboard
the Great Britannia now?!
[CHARLY OP E]
Lady Monica Krushevsky,
the honorable Knight of 12.
[BISMARCK] Very well! In that
case, I'm taking the Galahad!
[KANON] You still can't
contact the Mordred?
[RADIO A]
No, my lord.
Although I think she's
headed for Kamine Island.
[SCHNEIZEL]
I see.
That means she must have
just received the intelligence
and is on her way
to His Majesty.
[SCHNEIZEL] Along with
Suzaku? No, this is...
[SCHNEIZEL]
My apologies, Lady Kaguya.
The meeting will have
to be postponed.
We need to go to
Kamine Island at once.
[KAGUYA] I see. Then we
shall go with you, as well.
[gasps]
[KAGUYA] There's only
one person I can think of
who would be attacking
the Britannian emperor
in this situation.
I believe we all
know who that is.
I agree, Lady Kaguya.
That changes things.
We have a few points to
verify before we go on.
We can continue the meeting once
this matter has been settled.
[LELOUCH] If anyone wishes
to stop me, let them try!
If there's anyone who can
go beyond my despair!
[BISMARCK]
Our own forces turning on us.
I can't tell friend from foe,
and I can't just
destroy them all. Hm?
[BISMARCK]
Anya!
Surely you aren't
part of this, too?
[ANYA]
So, the Knight of One
is behind this traitorous
coup d'etat?!
What's that?!
[EMPEROR laughs]
[BISMARCK]
Don't jump to conclusions!
[ANYA]
How can I trust you?!
[BISMARCK] The enemy
is from Shikine Island!
Monica can testify to it!
I understand now.
Forgive me, Lord Bismark.
All I ask of you is
your recognition.
How damaged is your knightmare?
[ANYA] My air combat
mobility is dropping,
but perhaps I can intercept the
rebel forces on the ground.
[BISMARCK] Understood. I'll
defend the royal flagship.
You're quite the actress,
aren't you?
We don't have time to explain
things to Bismarck right now.
Since I questioned his loyalty,
he didn't question mine.
Putting him on the defensive.
That's just the sort of "flash"
I'd expect from
Marianne the Flash.
And it's just perfect
for Lelouch's mother.
So, what comes next?
[C.C.]
Hm?
[ANYA] Well, we have
to save him, don't we?
God! Hear me now!
The time has come
to settle this!
[LELOUCH]
You're wrong.
[LELOUCH] You lift your
voice to call upon God,
but it's not God you need
to settle things with,
Charles zi Britannia...
It's me... your son!
And how will you
challenge me?
Neither gun, nor sword,
will have any effect on me.
Nor will the power
of your Geass.
Nothing you do can kill me!
[LELOUCH]
But I don't need to kill you.
By coming to this
parallel realm,
you've already
ensured my victory.
[EMPEROR]
Huh?
[EMPEROR gasps]
[EMPEROR]
You've sealed the exit?!
[LELOUCH] Yes. You, I,
and the power of Geass
are now sealed in
this space together.
And, If you can no longer
interfere with the real world,
then all your plans will
be meaningless in the end.
May as well be dead!
Lelouch!
[LELOUCH] This system which you
created has become a prison
which now holds your
own soul captive!
Now, let us repent! Suffering
together for all eternity!
[LELOUCH] Now I see. Perhaps
I did choose the wrong path.
Perhaps Suzaku was
right all along.
It's the means that
are important.
But I can't back down now.
For Euphy and Shirley.
Nunnally, and Rolo.
That's right. I must face him!
I have to wager everything
I am against this man!
Charles, the Emperor
of Britannia!
It doesn't matter what
happens to me in the end,
but I must win!