[C.C.]
The Chinese Federation:
An alliance of nations
boasting the largest
population on the planet.
But the truth is, it can be
called a doddering old man.
The symbol of this
alliance is the empress.
The ruling class, which controls
society from within her shadow,
has grown exceedingly
tyrannical, while poverty
and stagnation
have sapped the life
from the nation's people.
When the Black
Knights fled Japan,
they sought refuge in this
neighboring federation.
The high eunuchs, the most
powerful men at the time,
lent the Japanese people the
man-made island of Horai,
built for tidal power generation
off the Jiangsu Province
on the coast of the Yellow Sea.
Even though this arrangement
was worked out well in advance,
all the political
implications of the deal
will not become apparent
until a later time.
[MINAMI]
Man, the Federation's laying
a lot of recognition on us!
[SUGIYAMA] There was that
whole bit with Sawasaki, too.
Think they're pro-Japanese?
The High Eunuchs, you mean?
Asahina! Don't you know?
The High Eunuchs may be guys,
but they've got no
jewels down below!
That's enough!
You'll get us in trouble
for saying stuff like that!
Aw, chill out!
[OHGI]
Hey!
I need a hand off-loading
the Knightmares.
What? They're here already?
Something's gotta be going
on behind the scenes
for India to be giving us
this much cooperation,
[OHGI] No, I think it's
that they're serious.
They want their independence
from the Chinese
Federation, as well.
[MINAMI]
Rakshata mentioned that, too.
[TAMAKI] Considering the
place is nowhere's ville.
[KID giggling]
C'mon! Hurry!
[DIETHARD]
We've finished picking out
staff leader candidates.
Should we assign them
to the Ikaruga for now?
[ZERO] Yes. That leaves us
with the municipal leaders.
[DIETHARD]
Correct.
Let's work with the intelligence
section and get that set up.
Now then, if you'll excuse me.
Are you sure that we
can depend on Diethard?
He acts on his own,
like what he did with Sayoko.
[ZERO] On the contrary,
he's easy to read.
[KALLEN]
Huh?
[ZERO]
In that man's mind,
he's trying to turn Zero
into a symbol for God.
Going from there, you can
guess what actions he'll take.
Besides, he has a useful talent
for manipulating information.
All right. That just
about does it.
That only leaves
the combat carrier.
You're installing
the Gawain's system
onto the Ikaruga, aren't you?
I used the same
on Shinkirou, too.
The Gawain's main
body was so damaged
when we salvaged
it from the sea.
And what about the
unit that sank with it?
The one being called
the Knight Gigafortress?
I tried to find
that myself, however...
[KALLEN]
You seriously want to take down
the Chinese
Federation's capital?
[LELOUCH] In such a way that
we won't be viewed as invaders.
If we overthrow Luoyang,
we clear a lot of conditions
for defeating Britannia.
[sighs]
[KALLEN]
He seems to be okay now.
I don't know what was happening
with him at that time.
[LELOUCH]
What is it?
Wha-?!
[KALLEN screams]
[thudding]
Tell me something, Lelouch.
Why'd you come back to us?
Kallen, when this is over,
will you then return
with me to Ashford?
[KALLEN]
Uh?
Cuz I'm...
[C.C.]
Tabasco?
[KALLEN, LELOUCH]
Uh! Huh?
[LELOUCH]
How long have you been there?
It needs Tabasco, but all
we have is hot sesame oil.
What should I do?
I wouldn't know.
I wouldn't neither.
[beeping]
[KAGUYA]
Master Zero,
please come to
the Ikaruga, hurry!
We've got trouble!
[C.C.]
Huh?
[ZERO]
What?! A political marriage?
Yes. I received an invitation
to the wedding through
the Sumeragi Conglomerate.
The bride-to-be is the empress,
icon of the Chinese Federation.
I'm her good friend,
and she wants me to attend.
[TOHDOH] And the groom is to be
the first prince of Britannia.
[RAKSHATA] That one
they call Odysseus.
It's too soon to activate
the plan we've set up.
I didn't expect that the
High Eunuchs would--
[ZERO]
No. This is a Britannian plot.
What do we do under
the circumstance?
[ZERO]
The worst possible situation.
[LELOUCH] Tsk! And I was going
to move in and grab the empress
before they had a chance to!
I never imagined
that mediocre man
could act so quickly!
Aw, why worry about it?
It's not as if we're involved
with Britannia any more!
What?!
We've been kicked out.
Have you forgotten?
Um...
But they haven't exonerated
us of our crimes, have they?
However, a political marriage...
There's always the possibility
that the Chinese Federation
might attack us.
And what then?!
The Black Knights are wrapped up
and given as a wedding present?!
Actually, that's an
apt way to put it.
You're sure developing
a useless ability there.
We're in big trouble here!
We're in no position to sit
around and make jokes!
[RAKSHATA]
Which is why...
[OHGI We're discussing
the matter at this moment!
Zero, the one behind this...
[ZERO]
Yes. There's another person.
The one who, overnight,
made this fiendish move
in order to reverse their
embittered relationship
with the Chinese Federation.
They would dare barter away the
empress to the Britannians?
[CROWD chatters]
[chuckles]
[whimpers]
Tell me, did the
empress willingly
consent to this marriage?
That's what they said, so we
can only take their word for it.
Besides, this arrangement
may be the path to peace.
True enough.
Today, let's just be good
guests and enjoy ourselves.
[GINO]
Suzaku! Look, I found it!
This is that charred newt stuff
you told me about, isn't it?
So, how do I eat it?
That's a decoration
made out of food.
Decoration? But didn't
I see you eat a bird
like this earlier
in the reception?
Do you mean the
Chinese phoenix?
Oh, that's what it was, hm?
I thought it was meat,
but it was really carrot--
--[beeping]
--Huh?
[GINO] Is this made out of
potato? I mean, I can eat it...
Excuse me, Lord Alstreim,
are you accessing your e-mails
here in the reception hall?
No. I'm memorizing something.
[CECILE]
Oh. That's a diary?
Well then, you're recording,
not memorizing.
Uh, Lloyd, I have a serious
question to ask you:
Am I still your fiancée or not?
You're, um... We didn't
call it off, did we?
This is a rare picture.
I figured you'd skip
the celebration party
and just attend the
ceremony tomorrow.
Occasionally, Suzaku gets
angry with me and says
that I ought to behave
like a betrothed man.
And this young woman
right here is the issue.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name's Milly Ashford.
Pleasure's mine. I am
dumbfounded to find Lloyd
showing interest
in anything human.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I must be growing up!
Allow me to introduce
Earl Kanon Maldini,
Prince Schneizel's aide-de-camp.
Public and private.
Huh? Uh...
[KANON]
I'm kidding.
[gasps]
It so happens the prince
has a preference
for unusual things.
Which includes myself.
[ANNOUNCER] Announcing the
arrival of the prime minister
of the Holy Britannian Empire!
Second prince Schneizel!
[MILLY]
It can't be... Nina!
My, I never thought my
younger brother
would keep the company of
just one particular woman.
Uh-huh.
[FEMALE A]
Who is that girl?
[FEMALE B]
Isn't she the chief of Invogue?
[FEMALE C]
Yes, the prince's research team.
[FEMALE A]
She's awfully young.
[FEMALE D] A girl like
that should know her place.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Be strong.
Euphy always presented
herself grandly.
[NINA gasps]
Right.
[GINO] It's been
a while, Your Highness.
The Emperor has commanded
that we accept orders
from you while in this land.
Three of the Rounds at court?
How splendid. Although...
[GINO]
Hm?
What, sir?
[SCHNEIZEL]
This is a celebration!
Relax a bit and have some fun.
[GINO]
Understood, sir!
Suzaku, I trust everyone
at school is doing well?
Yup. You see?
Hi, there!
Huh? Milly, it's you!
[XIANG-LIN] A secret
agreement has already been
set up between Prince
Schneizel and the High Eunuchs.
When she's married,
they'll cede our
territory to them.
He'll then grant
the High Eunuchs
titles of Britannian nobility.
Nobility? They would sell
off their country for that?
And our people?
[SYMPATHIZER B]
Death to the High Eunuchs.
[SYMPATHIZER C]
We've got to stop this wedding,
even if it means putting
our plan into action early.
[XIANG-LIN]
But if we stage a coup,
Britannia's going
to declare war.
Either we ensure peace,
or we do not.
[grunts]
[JAILER]
But, Your Majesty,
this man broke the law by trying
to save the life of an inmate.
[EMPRESS]
Yes, but...
I get brought medicine
when I'm sick,
and the person who
brings it isn't punished.
[JAILER] There's no comparing
that prisoner with you,
Your Majesty.
[GAO HAI]
Don't argue!
The banquet will
be starting soon!
Do as Her Majesty commands!
[JAILER] If he's taken to face
the law, he'll be executed!
[gasps]
But that's wrong!
[JAILER]
Uh?
[EMPRESS]
That's wrong!
He was doing something good,
so he shouldn't
die because of it!
[JAILER]
Uh! Well...you see...
[EMPRESS]
Officer's school?
[XING-KE]
Yes.
That's how I'll use the
life that you spared.
I wish to protect
you in any way I can.
I would like to go too.
To the outside.
Outside?
Outside of the forbidden city.
To school or
maybe to the sea.
Where you can find
all kinds of hot,
yummy food and lots
of friends to make.
Yes, very well.
[EMPRESS]
Huh?
[XING-KE] One day,
if you still wish,
I will take you away
from here, Your Majesty.
[EMPRESS]
Really?!
[XING-KE] It's my
way of thanking you
for sparing my life.
[EMPRESS]
Hm?
[XING-KE] This is how we
make promises outside the city.
[EMPRESS]
Hm.
[XING-KE]
Mm-hm.
An everlasting promise.
[EMPRESS]
For all time.
Either I protect her Majesty
or I allow an alliance
to ensure peace.
[ODYSSEUS]
At any rate,
I'm certainly glad this
arrangement all worked out!
I'm no good at fighting.
Your Highness, will the Emperor
be attending the wedding?
He informed me at the banquet
back in the homeland
that he would attend.
Miss Kaguya Sumeragi!
The representative of the
Sumeragi Conglomerate!
Kaguya? What?!
[CROWD gasps]
It's Zero! How dare he!
That redhead with him,
isn't she the Guren pilot?
[MALE A]
Who invited him here?!
[MALE B]
To a place like this?!
[MALE C]
He's a terrorist!
Well, well, well!
[LELOUCH]
Schneizel!
So you are the puppet
master behind all this!
[NINA] You're nearly ready
to graduate, aren't you?
[MILLY giggles] I suppose
I should finish, huh?
But I'm happy for you.
You seem to be doing
well for yourself.
Frankly, I'm relieved.
You're relieved?
Uh-huh.
If anything happens, you can
come to me for advice.
Just stop that.
Huh?
[NINA]
Milly, I like you, I really do.
However, I hate women
who have no depth to them.
[MILLY gasps]
Princess Euphemia
didn't abandon me.
Instead of running away,
she risked her own
life to save mine.
She was the only
one who helped me.
[MILLY]
And I'll help you, too.
[NINA grunts]
[NINA] Will you stop
spouting pity for me!
You're always playing
around as the campus queen,
and you hide behind Ashford
as if it's a shield!
It's the same with your
engagement to Professor Lloyd!
You always look down on me,
acting like some
self-appointed guardian
while you swim in
your own hypocrisy!
I've changed! It's time
you acknowledge that!
Kaguya!
[gasps]
Well, our wedding present has
arrived of it's own accord.
My, this worked out wonderfully!
You're giving
them Kaguya, too?
Put that girl out of your mind.
Her crimes warrant
the death penalty.
[EMPRESS]
No, you can't! That's wrong!
This isn't Britannia!
[XIA WANG]
Your Majesty,
the Black Knights are the
ones who killed Gao Hai.
Please, don't get involved and
just leave the politics to us.
Isn't that what
you've always done,
let us handle things our way?
But, she's a friend.
Can we please stop
quarrelling now?
Today is a day
of celebration, is it not?
[CHENG ZHONG]
Eh! But, sir...
[SCHNEIZEL] Miss Sumeragi,
will you refrain from having
Zero accompany you to
the wedding tomorrow?
I suppose.
I don't have much
of a choice, do I?
If that is the wish of the
Prime Minister of Britannia,
then withdraw!
[LELOUCH]
So, Schneizel...
you appear right before me?
Hmph. As watchful
as ever, I see.
[KAGUYA]
Suzaku Kururugi?
[SUZAKU]
Uh!
[KAGUYA]
Do you remember me?
We're cousins, you and I.
Of course I do.
[KAGUYA] We're the
last remaining survivors
of the six houses
of Kyoto, aren't we?
Taizou Kirihara and the
others supported terrorists.
Nothing could have
stayed their executions.
But this is different.
Cousin, did you forget
that Master Zero
once saved your life?
[gasps]
[KAGUYA] Do you plan to execute
someone you owe your life to?
There's no comparison!
Oh, how sad.
It's a good thing we're
not able to kill anybody
merely with the words we say.
[ZERO]
Prince Schneizel.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hm?
[ZERO] Would you care
for a game of chess?
Chess?
[ZERO] If I win, I'd like
to have Sir Kururugi.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?!
What?!
[ZERO] I want give him
to you, Lady Kaguya.
Oh, that would be an
absolutely marvelous present!
[ZERO] Enjoy your
anticipation of it.
[LELOUCH] If I can
get Suzaku out of here,
I can use my Geass
on all the others.
A checkmate that would
turn everything around.
I'll agree to your terms,
however, if you lose,
I want you to remove your
mask and show me your face.
--[LELOUCH] Agreed.
--[KALLEN gasps]
What a fine evening
of entertainment
this has turned into!
[ODYSSEUS]
Surely we don't have to watch
from a separate room
away from the show?
He's playing a terrorist.
Something could happen, sir.
That's ridiculous.
It's my husband
who's going to win.
[ODYSSEUS chuckles]
[ODYSSEUS]
I understand how you feel,
Miss Sumeragi, but I can't
imagine anyone but my brother,
Schneizel, winning this game.
[ANYA] This is the ace
of the Black Knights.
Pilot of the Guren.
Yeah, The one from before?
She's a lot prettier
than her wanted poster.
That's my kind of woman.
[gasps]
He is good.
His Highness is losing.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hm...
[ZERO]
Oh, I didn't expect you
to turn the tables
on me so quickly.
[LELOUCH]
My brother was, and still is,
a master of this game.
He's the only person
I could never beat.
However, that was
eight years ago.
It's your king!
[ZERO]
If the king doesn't lead,
how can he expect his
subordinates to follow?
Impressive strategy.
In fact... I'll do the same.
[ZERO gasps]
[CROWD murmurs]
[NINA]
Huh?
I'm on the edge of my seat
wondering who will win this now.
Well, They're evenly matched.
Stubborn competition.
Practically a fight!
[ZERO]
So...
You can't advance
any further, can you?
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hmm...
We'll get into a threefold
repetition at this rate.
[ZERO]
It wasn't my intention,
but shall we
declare this a draw?
I think not.
[ZERO]
Hm?
[SCHNEIZEL]
You would do well not to
underestimate the
white king, my friend.
[ZERO]
You wouldn't!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Checkmate.
But that means if Zero
moves his king forward...
Then he'll capture...
Prince Schneizel's king!
Oh, that's too big of a joke!
He's deliberately
losing the game?
[ZERO]
What is this?
You're simply handing
me a victory?
[LELOUCH]
If I accept this invitation,
I'll be giving in to his intent!
I can't allow this!
This humiliation!
[CROWD gasps]
With no hesitation whatsoever,
the emperor would
have grabbed it.
[ZERO gasps]
[SCHNEIZEL]
I've now learned just a bit
about what kind of man
you really are, Zero.
[LELOUCH]
Schneizel.
You dare look down
on me like that?!
[ZERO]
Uh?!
Zero! Princess Euphemia
will be avenged!
[CROWD gasps]
Stop it, Nina! Drop the knife!
[NINA screams]
Why are you stopping me?!
You of all people
should understand
since you were Princess
Euphemia's knight!
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
That's right. Then why...?
You're just an Eleven
after all, aren't you?!
[KALLEN]
Nina!
[NINA] Why, Kallen?!
You're half Britannian,
and yet you choose to
protect that monster!
No. That's incorrect.
I'm Japanese, Nina.
No you're not.
You're an Eleven.
You're an Eleven, and you
pretended to be my friend?!
[gasps]
[NINA] Give her back to me!
Give back Princess Euphemia!
I needed her! She was
a goddess to me!
[SUZAKU]
Nina...
Zero...killed her...but you...
[SUZAKU] This is just another
tragedy that Zero has caused.
[NINA whimpers]
Oh, Nina...
[MILLY gasps]
I'm sorry. About everything.
However...
[MILLY] Kallen. You haven't
changed at all.
Even during the Black Rebellion,
you were worried about us.
Meanwhile...I...
[LELOUCH]
I...will never turn back!
My profound apologies, Zero.
Let's put an end to
our little game here.
Now that I've confirmed
my suspicions,
I'd like to remind you to not
attend the ceremony tomorrow.
Otherwise, a game of chess
won't save you next time.
[ODYSSEUS]
Have no fear.
[EMPRESS]
That's right.
I'm marrying this man tomorrow.
And once we're married,
I'll be leaving the
forbidden city with him.
I will go to Britannia
as a hostage.
Never dreamed this
was how I would finally
reach the outside. It will
be my first and last time.
I won't be able to return
here again, will I?
I... I...
[gasps]
[XING-KE]
We ask this question!
By the voice of heaven,
the roar of the land,
and the hearts of the people!
How does this marriage represent
the will of the
Chinese Federation?!
Terrorists?!
No, I think they've got
a coup d'etat going on!
Xing-ke, have you
lost your mind?!
Be silent, Zhao Hao!
In the name of my
fellow countrymen,
I challenge the
legality of this wedding!
[GUARD 1]
Hold him back!
[XING-KE]
It's strange...
[GUARD 2, XING-KE grunt]
[XING-KE] As much as I pray
to save my starving people,
I can only think about
Her Majesty's welfare.
[XING-KE]
Right now... I must--!
Cut off the broadcast!
[TV ANNOUNCER]
This is a terrible situation--
[SHIRLEY]
Aah!
[RIVALZ]
Oh, no! What about Milly?!
Meow?
Lady Kaguya,
let's get out of here.
What the...?
--Let's go!
--All right!
[XING-KE grunting]
[XIA WANG]
Seize him!
We can't let anything happen to
the Britannians, otherwise...
it'll be disastrous!
[XING-KE grunts]
[GUARD 4 groans]
[GUARD 5]
Traitor!
You think the empress
belongs to you and no other?!
[XING-KE gasps]
That's right.
I have no idea
whether my action
is in accordance with
Her Majesty's wishes.
She may not even have
the faintest memory
of what occurred six years ago.
But no matter.
I made an everlasting
promise to Her Majesty
in return for sparing my life!
A vow I swore in my heart!
I must... I must
save the empress!
I will take her...
to the outside world!
[EMPRESS]
Xing-ke!
[XING-KE]
Huh?
[EMPRESS]
Xing-ke...!
Xing-ke! Xing-ke! Xing-ke!
[XING-KE]
She does... She remembers!
In my heart...
...there is no more doubt!
Xing-ke!
[gasps]
[ZERO]
I appreciate this, Xing-ke!
You've made it so much
easier for me to make my move.
Oh! T-That man, too?!
[XING-KE] Zero, what's the
meaning of this?
[ZERO]
Don't move!
[whimpers]
[gasps]
What a wretched coward!
Zero. My warning
fell on deaf ears.
[XING-KE] I thought the
Black Knights owed us
for what we did
for them in Area 11.
[ZERO] Which his why
I'm ruining this wedding.
Exactly as you people wanted.
The only thing is, I'm taking
the bride with me!
Xing-ke!
Your Majesty!
[growls]
You filthy scum!
[ZERO]
Oh, am I?
[ZERO laughs]
[V.V.]
Yes. If Zero's true objective...
...turns out to be here,
we're in trouble.
[JEREMIAH]
Yes.
Is that why you've made
preparations for me?
[V.V.]
It is.
[JEREMIAH]
Thank you very much.
Once I'm properly adjusted, C.C.
and Lelouch will be
no match for me.
Your expectations
of Jeremiah Gottwald
will be more than satisfied,
I promise you!
[LELOUCH] Even if they try
to move now, it's too late.
The empress, the symbol
of the Chinese Federation,
has fallen into my hands.
Xing-ke, the High Eunuchs,
Schneizel, too...
Let them all dance to my plan!
I'm through
positioning my pieces.
This is no game of chess.
I intend to checkmate the nation
known as the Chinese Federation!
And once I have, I'm coming
for him! I'll possess
the power to confront the
emperor of Britannia!
And for that, I swear I'll...!