[C.C.] In this world, evil can
arise from the best intentions.
And there is good, which can
come from evil intentions.
How then should Lelouch's
actions be taken?
Every man has his day of
judgment, does he not?
[C.C.]
Geass...
He who uses this inhuman power
will find his heart isolated,
whether he wants
it that way or not.
Thus, he plummets into the abyss
that lies between good and evil.
But if a man can climb out
of that abyss into the light,
then that man has
the soul of a king.
[LELOUCH] All right, first,
I just want to confirm this:
Are you my enemy or my ally?
Where's this coming from?
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
[LELOUCH] Mao's Geass lets him
get right into someone's head
and hear what they're
thinking and planning.
I've got that right, don't I?
[C.C.]
Yes.
The way Geass manifests is
different for each person.
If Mao concentrates,
he can hear thoughts
up to 500 meters away.
And he can read clear
down to your subconscious
if he wants to.
For someone like you
who fights with his head,
he's the worst possible enemy.
[LELOUCH]
Five hundred meters...
Well, it doesn't really
come as a surprise to me.
I knew there must be others
who had the power of Geass.
Did you make a
contract with him?
[C.C.]
Eleven years ago.
[LELOUCH]
So, he's my predecessor.
Is there some reason that this
forerunner is also my enemy?
[C.C.]
Mao's after me.
He may be your enemy,
but he's not targeting you.
Yeah, well I can see that.
He could have revealed
my true identity
and told the police or
the military who I am,
but the only one he
told was Shirley.
Are there limits to his powers?
Mao's Geass is very potent.
He can use it as many
times as he wants,
and he doesn't need direct
eye contact like you do.
[LELOUCH]
Does he have any weakness?
If you press me,
I guess it's that he
can't turn his power off.
In a crowd, he hears
all the minds
roiling and writhing around him,
whether he wants to or not.
[overlapping voices]
--[more overlapping voices]
--[MAO gasping, panting]
[C.C.]
I understand, Mao.
Don't worry, Mao.
I'm not going to die.
Mao! Mao!
Are you awake, Mao?
Oh, Mao, how silly of you!
C.C., I can't live without you.
[C.C]
See, Mao?
Wait for me, I'm coming to you!
[LELOUCH] If Mao read my
mind, then he already knows
my weak points, and that's
where he'll strike.
It's been a long time since we
spent time by ourselves, huh?
You know, even Sayoko needs a
little time off now and again.
Starting today, I'll be
staying home for a while.
[NUNNALLY] Lately you've been
out of the house so much,
I was curious, have you
found some really fun game
to play or something?
Sort of.
My current opponent's
pretty hard to beat.
[NUNNALLY giggles]
That's funny.
Only our big brother Schneizel
would ever make you say
something like that.
[WEAPONS DEALER]
Sorry, but I can't sell you one
without a permit...
It's illegal.
Besides, you're from the
Chinese Federation, aren't you?
[MAO] Uh... true. But you sell
them to the Black Knights.
--[WEAPONS DEALER gasps]
--[MAO] Last Tuesday,
twenty-three hundred hours.
Your contact was named "Wolf."
An alias, of course.
Who are you?!
You will kindly accommodate me.
Won't you now?
[LELOUCH]
And?
I know that you want to
protect your sister and all,
but you can't just sit around
here and wait for him!
I've got the Black Knights
hunting for him.
[C.C.] What if he's not in
the ghetto like you think?
What if he's right here
in the Tokyo Settlement?
Then you'll have wasted
all that precious time
when you could just
use me as bait.
I'm Mao's target,
so I should be--
Tell me, if I keep
using my Geass,
will I become like him?
[C.C. gasps]
Or did he end up the way he
is because he didn't fulfill
his contract with you?
The more you use your Geass,
the more powerful it becomes.
Those who cannot
control the power
are ultimately ravaged
and consumed by it.
And even though you knew
everything about that,
you still offered
these contracts?!
To me?!
And to Mao?!
That's right.
[LELOUCH]
You're a cruel girl.
I don't know why anyone
would chase after you.
Mao couldn't fulfill
his contract with you,
so you cut him loose.
What were the terms
of the contract?
You're a monster!
[C.C. gasps]
[LELOUCH] Why didn't you finish
it when you cut him off?!
You should have taken his
power back, or taken his life!
Because you left things
half-finished, Shirley was--!
[C.C.] We should split up
while we're dealing with Mao.
Starting today, I'll
stay in the next hall.
You can't.
The student council and the
culture clubs meet there.
[C.C.]
I don't care about that.
You work it out.
[SUZAKU]
A medical check up?
[CECILE]
Just regulations.
It's required for
all Knightmare pilots.
I understand.
Good. Tomorrow then,
after your school gets out.
[SUZAKU]
Right. Thanks.
Oh, Miss Cecile...
Do know of any way I can get
in to see Princess Euphemia?
[CECILE]
Huh? You want to meet her?
Forget it.
You have to be at least
a Knight of Honor
to get an audience with her.
But an earl could arrange it,
if he really wanted to.
Who? Me?
[CECILE]
Yes.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
Lloyd, you're an earl?!
You never told me that!
[LLOYD laughs]
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
[CECILE]
The prodigal son of nobles...
He can't really
separate work from play.
Wow...
[LELOUCH] You know, it would
be just for a few days.
If you can keep the
clubhouse off limits,
that would really help out.
[MILLY] Well, it's not
like I can't do it, but...
Say, did someone find
out you're a prince?
[LELOUCH] Hopefully, that
secret's still safe.
Only the Ashford family knows
that I'm still here
and still alive.
[MILLY]
The all-knowing Ashfords...
Is something wrong?
Oh, Lelouch, they've got another
blind date set up for me.
I may not be able to
wriggle out of this one.
What do you think I
should do about it?
Well... That is...
[SHIRLEY]
Madame President!
--[MILLY] Hm?
--[LELOUCH gasps]
[MILLY]
Shirley!
Were you back at
morning practice?
[SHIRLEY] Yeah, it just
started again today.
You can't stay sad forever!
[MILLY chuckles]
I should take lessons from
you on positive thinking!
[SHIRLEY laughs]
What are you talking about?
You're way more...
Huh?
Aren't you're the boy from...
You go to school here, too?
Are you putting me on?
We're in the same classes.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?!
No! I don't think we are!
Hm... Are we?
Please, that's enough now.
Shirley, we're ready to start!
I'll be right there!
See you later, Prez!
[MILLY]
Mm-hm...
What was that about?
[LELOUCH]
We... had a little fight.
So she's playing strangers?
Oh, that is so cute.
Sorry, but could you
play along with us?
Until she gets over it, y'know.
[MILLY chuckles]
I guess I could.
Think it'll take long?
[LELOUCH]
Yes, I'm afraid so.
[PUNK groans]
[C.C.] I'm not looking
for a refrain dealer!
I said, a Chinese guy
named Mao, did you hear me?!
[PUNK]
Believe me, I have no idea.
The only Chinese around here
are pushers or gang labor!
Go ask the cops or something!
[C.C.]
I don't like cops!
[PUNK groans] Then ask
the Black Knights about him!
They're all over
the underground;
they're wired into the
settlement and the ghettos.
Everyone tells me
the same thing!
[PUNK]
'Cause it's obvious!
[SHIRLEY]
Huh? That's strange!
Where is it?
What's the matter Shirley?
what are you looking for?
My diary. It's gone.
I can't find it anywhere.
[SOPHIE]
Huh? Did you take it somewhere?
[SHIRLEY laughs]
'Course not!
[INOUE]
Right. I'm sorry, Zero.
We haven't found
this Mao guy yet.
[LELOUCH]
I see.
Should we check our contacts
in the Kyoto network?
[LELOUCH] No, just stay
with the Kanto block.
If you come up with
any leads, let me know.
Yes, will do.
[LELOUCH]
All right, I'll get back to you.
[LELOUCH] If I get
within 500 meters of Mao,
he can read my mind.
That's what he wants.
But knowing that, I should be
able to guess his next move.
[LELOUCH growls]
I could put him in check,
if I just had one--
[C.C.]
Missing piece?
You and I are thinking
exactly the same thing.
So it seems.
Then we should work together
on this, don't you agree?
--[LELOUCH] I do. Hm?
--[phone rings]
[ringing continues]
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
Yes?
[MAO]
It's me, Lulu!
C.C.'s there too, isn't she?
I want to talk to her
alone. Put her on.
[VILETTA groans]
Are you waking up now?
[VILETTA]
Yes...
What were you doing in that
place? Passed out like that?
What's your name?
I, uh... My name is...?
[OHGI gasps]
[VILETTA]
What is my name?
You don't remember?!
What about Zero? You were
talking about him before!
[VILETTA]
Who's Zero?
[OHGI gasps, groans]
What am I doing?! I practically
betray him, and why?!
But I don't know anything...
[gasps]
...nothing at all.
Uh... Sorry.
I was able to undress
you with my eyes closed,
but getting your clothes
back on wasn't so...
But I turned up the heat, so
I thought you'd be all right.
[VILETTA]
Mm. Thank goodness.
[OHGI]
Uh?
Anyone could have
picked me up out there,
but I got someone nice.
[OHGI] Huh?
[VILETTA chuckles]
[phone beeps]
You should be happy
about this, Lelouch.
We're finally going
our separate ways.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[C.C.]
I made up with Mao.
You're betraying me?
Are you actually saying that?
When were you my friend? Never.
We were just
co-conspirators that's all.
[LELOUCH]
Wait!
[C.C.]
Well, here's a surprise.
You sound just like Mao.
[LELOUCH]
C.C...
You know way too
much about me now.
I can't let you walk
away like this.
[LELOUCH]
Don't go!
C.C.! Stay here with me!
[LELOUCH chuckles]
Geass does not work on me.
Didn't I mention that?
[LELOUCH grunts]
[C.C.] Don't worry, I won't
tell anyone about you.
You can keep your Geass, too.
And Mao won't
bother you anymore.
He'll never cross your path...
So all your obstacles are
gone: Congratulations.
And farewell.
The test results came out fine.
Though you seem to pay
extreme attention to
discipline and to weighing
the value of human life.
Is that going to cause problems?
[DOCTOR] These are positive
traits for a soldier.
Do you think subconsciously,
you're comparing
yourself to your father?
[BOTH gasp]
That may be the underlying
cause of your insecurity.
It's quite common in the
children of famous people.
Your father. Genbu Kururugi, the
former prime minister of Japan--
He was a great man.
[CHIBA]
Urabe and the others are late.
Well, this sure is an ironic
meeting place, isn't it?
The grave of Prime
Minister Kururugi.
The traitor who told us
to fight to the end,
then committed suicide himself.
Enough.
General Katase also
committed suicide,
and he was a true patriot.
[SCOUT]
Fugitive Tohdoh, identified.
All units, prepare to move in.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, my lord.
Yes, I've read through
your proposal for
reorganizing the Black Knights.
[LELOUCH]
I've got a few changes,
but overall, I like where
you're going with this.
I'll run it by Ohgi tomorrow.
Thanks, I appreciate that.
[LELOUCH] Next draft, I'd
like you to insert a chart
that forecasts how the
cell-based structure
will be implemented.
That's all.
So that was the final
test; I guess I passed.
[LELOUCH] Diethard...
Though he's Britannian,
he's proving even more
useful than I'd hoped.
Still, he could be a spy;
I can't rule that out yet.
Hm?
Right...
It recorded them.
[MAO]
C.C.!
Your mind is so quiet!
It's the only one I can't read!
You really are
the best there is!
As childish as ever, I see.
[MAO] I'm a prince
on a white stallion!
And a prince has to
rescue the princess!
[laughs]
Does that make you happy, C.C.?
Mao, we talked
about this before.
I told you that you and I--
[MAO]
Those were all lies... Lies!
C.C., you love me, and
this is how I know...
[C.C.]
Thank you, Mao.
Mao... Mao.
Stop it!
[MAO]
Be quiet!
[C.C.]
Don't listen to them.
Just listen to the
sound of my voice.
That's it...
Since my mind is the
only one you can't read,
and you can only be happy
when you're with me...
I will stay with you always.
Yes... I'm right here.
So you don't need to worry.
[MAO]
C.C., you're the only one!
The only one I want, forever!
Lelouch doesn't matter at all.
If you just come with me--
Stop it!
[MAO gasps]
I should have done this
a long, long time ago!
[gunshot]
[beep]
[MAO]
It's me, C.C.
[C.C.]
Mao.
[MAO] I'll be at
Clovisland. Come alone.
[C.C.] Ugh, You're as
selfish as ever, I see.
[MAO]
If you don't come,
I'll just have to tell the
police who Lelouch really is.
I can have him eliminated
any time I want.
You should be happy
about this, Lelouch.
We're finally going
our separate ways.
[LELOUCH] She comes and
goes like the wind.
I can't read her.
I can't fathom how such
a twisted girl thinks.
Idiot!
[C.C. groans]
I knew it! I knew you
couldn't pull the trigger!
That's 'cause you
really love me, C.C.!
[laughs]
You're wrong! I was just using
you right from the start!
[MAO gasps]
What are you saying?
You shouldn't tell lies like
that, you really shouldn't.
[C.C. groans]
[MAO]
Lies are very, very wicked!
Wicked lies!
--[gunshots]
--[C.C. groaning]
[MAO]
Don't worry.
I understand!
[C.C. groans]
C.C., you must listen to me.
I've built a big, brand
new house in Australia.
A very quiet, white,
immaculate special house.
[C.C. groans]
But to get to Australia,
you'll need to take an airplane,
and there isn't very much room.
The thing is, C.C.,
you're a little too
big to bring on plane.
[C.C. gasps]
So, that's why...
I'm going to make you compact!
It'll take no time at all!
Is this your revenge?
You're punishing me?
Oh, no. I'm not.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not,
I'm not at all!
I'm showing you my gratitude!
[LELOUCH]
So this is the place you picked.
A place where there'd be no one
else's thoughts to bother you.
That narrowed it way down.
[MAO]
Lelouch!
[C.C. gasps]
Since your Geass has a total
maximum range of 500 meters,
it can't reach me
here at Tokyo Tower.
[MAO laughs]
That's true, that's very true!
But what can you do
from so far away, hm?
After taking all that trouble
to hack into the system,
what's your grand plan?
A remote control attack with
some battery-operated toys?
Or a tongue lashing to
lecture me into submission?
Aah, cat got your tongue now.
If you want C.C., then
you're gonna have to come--
Mao, think! You don't believe
C.C. is her real name, do you?
She never even
whispers it to anyone.
[MAO gasps]
Huh...?
But I know it, though.
She told me her true name.
Is that right, C.C.?
You never told me, ever, ever!
But you told it to him?!
[LELOUCH]
You know why?
Because C.C. is mine.
C.C. belongs to me,
in every possible way.
No! She doesn't!
She doesn't, she doesn't,
she doesn't!
She was mine long
before she met you!
I have gained every
single thing from her,
including all of the parts
that you have never seen.
[MAO gasps]
[LELOUCH]
All of them.
[MAO growls]
Lelouch...!
Face me!
Lelouch! Come here!
Come here so I can
look into your mind!
I'll see the truth.
I'll see what a liar you are!
Liar!
[LELOUCH]
Mao... You've lost.
What are you talking about?!
I don't care; I'm gonna
to be with C.C.!
--[overlapping thoughts]
--[MAO gasps]
[overlapping thoughts continue]
[MAO]
Is that Lelouch?
But he's too far away...
Sounds! Everywhere!
All those voices!
[COP 1]
Hold it right there!
Drop the weapon and surrender!
What are they doing here?!
[MAO gasps]
[COP 1]
Remain where you are!
Drop down your weapon
and raise your hands!
[MAO gasps]
It's the police!
Who contacted them?!
[MAO gasps]
[C.C. gasps]
Lelouch! What are
you doing here?
It can't be!
He was just at Tokyo Tower,
he can't be here now!
[LELOUCH]
Are you that slow?
That was all a recording.
That's a lie!
You-- You were talking
to me! Answering me!
[LELOUCH]
Your thoughts are simple.
Since you read minds, you've
never resorted to cunning.
You predicted every
one of my answers?!
Don't play games with me, punk!
If these cops arrest me,
I'll be back out in a heartbeat!
[overlapping thoughts]
[MAO]
Shut up! Just stop taunting me!
[LELOUCH chuckles] C.C. told me
you can't turn off your Geass.
And your reach is erratic.
If you don't concentrate,
the range gets very short.
[MAO] So you used the monitor
to keep me distracted?
Even so...
I can still defeat you;
I'll have you ruined!
[LELOUCH] The moment you
try is the moment you die.
Lelouch, wait! If I talk
to him, I can get through!
You think I'll die?!
Listen, cops, you know
who that guy is?!
He's the terrorist you want!
--He's--
--[COP] Fire!
Oh, Mao!
[MAO groans]
Zero...
[C.C.]
Mao was only 6 years old
when I made my
contract with him.
He was an orphan
who'd never known
the love of a parent.
He couldn't read or write.
And he knew nothing
of good and evil.
This is Echo-3.
I've released the hostage
into the ghetto as ordered.
[RADIO] What? Your orders were
to take her to the hospital!
[C.C.] When I gave the Geass
power to Mao, it isolated him.
In his mind, I became his
only friend and his lover,
though I was still
a perfect stranger.
I'm the only one he even
thought of as human.
I was Mao's entire world.
[LELOUCH]
C.C...
Listen to me, I won't
let Geass destroy me.
I will conquer its power
and bend it to my will...
And use it to change the world.
I'll fulfill your
desire and my own.
And I will complete the contract
that he couldn't achieve.
So, please...
[C.C.]
Lelouch, tell me.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[C.C.]
Are you trying to comfort me?
Pity me?
Or is this part
of your obsession?
It's a contract.
This time, it's from me to you.
Very well, then.
I accept your contract.
[LELOUCH] Now is the
time to move forward!
To smash Cornelia
and get the truth!
And to make a place for
Nunnally in this world.
These tiny battlefields
are meaningless now!
We're taking over
the Tokyo Settlement!
We'll expand our military
might and extend our contacts.
I'll use every
piece in the game.