[C.C.] Three great
powers control the world.
Two of them, the Holy
Britannian Empire
and the Chinese Federation
are trying to become one
through a political marriage.
This would be the
ultimate threat
to the United States of Japan.
That is why Zero has
acted by kidnapping
the Chinese Federation's
young empress,
the symbol of her nation.
Can dreams cut a
path through destiny?
Can passion triumph over fate?
Or are such things ephemeral,
like flower petals
fluttering in the breeze.
[GUESTS screaming]
[CHINA COMM] Lady Xiang-Lin,
the guests are fleeing
the reception hall
just as we predicted,
but we have reports that
Zero has shown up as well.
Zero! Section 3,
report your break-in status.
Master Xing-ke needs
back up at once.
[XIANG-LIN]
Could it be?
Is Zero using our plan
for his own purposes?
Xing-ke!
[grunts]
Zero! Will you release
Her Majesty or not?!
[ZERO] Xing-ke, do you
think you're able to free
the empress alone?
You're mistaken.
[ALL grunting]
[XING-KE] You even had a
Knightmare prepared for this?
[TOHDOH] Hmph. I never thought
the Zangetsu's first mission
would be to steal a
bride from a wedding.
[ZERO]
Tohdoh! Get Schneizel!
Right.
I'm on it.
He's already here.
Hands off the prince!
[TOHDOH]
Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
It can't be! Master Tohdoh?!
Flee while you can,
Your Highness!
I guess it can't
be helped, brother?
Yes, I think we should.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Schneizel!
We should go too;
leave it to the soldiers.
Yes.
[CHIBA] Zero! The operation's
on schedule.
[ZERO]
Good! Enter phase three!
We're on our way.
[BOTH panting]
Xing-ke!
Dammit!
[GUARDS yell]
[KALLEN, KAGUYA panting]
Yes! Now!
The same system
as the Guren?
So, it does work.
With this Zangetsu,
I can take on a class
one warrior like Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
So be it. I'll blow you aw--
[TOHDOH]
Think!
[TOHDOH] Will you shoot
at me in this position?
[gasps]
The Forbidden City!
[SUZAKU]
Are they?
[gasps]
[TOHDOH] Suzaku Kururugi,
taste defeat!
Kyoshiro Tohdoh! Not yet!
[TOHDOH]
Shadow Longsword!
He got my float unit!
[grunts] You can still
launch a direct attack?
[ZERO]
Tohdoh! Return to your unit.
You destroyed the
Lancelot's float unit,
so he can't pursue us.
That's enough for now.
We need you here.
[TOHDOH]
Understood.
Your Majesty, you'll soon be
outside the Forbidden City.
Huh?
[XING-KE grunts] Deploy the
Dragon Cavalry to pursue them.
[ZHAO HAO]
That is now our task;
you are relieved of duty!
[huffs]
[XIA WANG] Are they trying
to escape through a gap
in our radar
surveillance network?
Absurd. How could
they know that?
It's barely ten days
since they arived here,
there's no way for
them to find that out.
General Tohdoh,
we'll begin resupplying
Knightmares from
Chiba's Akatsuki.
[TOHDOH] Good.
Then resupply the Zangetsu
and Guren after we
return to the Ikaruga.
Okay, take the next left turn.
Is that correct?
[TAMAKI]
Whops, my mistake!
Idiot!
[KAGUYA, EMPRESS gasp]
Are you all right,
Your Majesty?
Are we outside
the palace?
Yes.
I'm sorry, I didn't expect
that your dream would come true
in such a violent
way like this, but...
[gasps] You remembered
about my dream, too!
You both did!
[grunts] They don't
know when to quit!
Get lost!
Now, take the next right.
No, we go straight here.
What? You know how to get there?
[C.C.]
Long ago, there's something I...
[ZERO] Our nation, the United
States of Japan, should be
thought of as just a part of a
giant union of united states.
Um.
[ZERO] Including the
United States of China.
And for that, we need you.
[KAGUYA]
The Indian Southern Province
has already promised support.
Mongolia and Burma will
probably move with them.
[ZERO]
This Union of United States
will form an axis
to oppose Britannia.
But, our nation's already
a federated system...
[ZERO]
All systems are limited!
That's why the high eunuchs
sold you to Britannia,
for their own ambition!
That is unforgivable!
Um, It's hard to
understand this but...
[KAGUYA]
Your Majesty?
[EMPRESS]
Huh?
[KAGUYA]
Is Li Xing-ke the one
you'd really like
to be married to?
[gasps]
Oh, no. He just made a promise.
As your fiance?
Well, I-I told him I wanted
to go outside six years ago.
It was that long ago?
He must be destined for you!
You, you think so?
That's great!
Are you sure you want
to leave her to Kaguya?
[ZERO] Since the
empress doesn't respond
to theoretical arguments.
You don't like that.
[ZERO]
It's hard to deal with.
Say, Zero,
have you come up with some
kind of position for me, yet?
[C.C.]
Hnm
[TAMAKI]
I'm wide open, man.
Maybe you can post me as finance
minister or head of banking.
How 'bout Grand
Minister of Partying.
I told you to quit making
fun of me like that!
Come on, we're old
buddies, right?
[ZERO] We'll discuss it
after we finish the mission.
[TAMAKI]
Huh?
What?! The bridge is gone?!
[BRIDGE GUARD] This is Forbidden
City Strike Force, unit four.
Target is currently
stopped at Shen Chun.
[ZHAO HAO]
They are such fools.
[LELOUCH chuckles]
They fell for it,
just as I thought
they would.
[ZERO]
Asahina!
[ASAHINA]
I'm on it!
All units, ready for attack.
[gasps]
An ambush?!
[BRIDGE GUARD]
Enemy troops! We're surrounded!
[XIA WANG]
What? Shoot them! Hurry!
[CHENG ZHONG]
No, wait! The empress!
[ASAHINA] Okay, let's try
out these new weapons.
They've taken out our
strike force, haven't they?
[ZHAO HAO]
How did you know that?
[XING-KE]
If I were in their place.
I'd hang back and stage an
ambush at the Shen Chun ravine.
[CHENG ZHONG]
And then?
[XING-KE] Then I'd join up
with my main force in Shao Pei.
Hmm.
Xing-ke, we're willing
to overlook your crimes
if you can bring
back our empress.
We'll even give
you a new weapon.
[gasps]
[LLOYD]
How is Prince Odysseus?
[SCHNEIZEL] He seems to
have calmed down at last.
He's resting.
[SUZAKU] Then once we've
replaced my float unit,
I can go after the empress.
No, we can't go there
unless requested
by the Chinese Federation.
I understand, but we're
missing our chance.
[ZERO] That went more
smoothly than I'd hoped.
Perhaps I should thank Xing-ke
for setting his
own plan in motion.
He's a talented strategist.
So, how did you find
out he was planning
a coup d'etat at the ceremony?
[KALLEN]
Hm?
[ZERO]
I was working on the same thing.
[C.C.] Including the
E.C.M. and the ambush?
[ZERO] Yes. While we
were setting our traps,
we found some of Xing-ke's
men setting theirs,
on the same escape route.
I see. Then you got them
to tell you their plan.
Did you have to
use a truth serum?
[ZERO]
Yes. It's called "Geass."
[C.C. sighs]
[ZERO] Is there news
from Horai Island?
[DIETHARD]
Reinforcements from India
have already arrived there.
[OHGI] We just have to return
and rendezvous with them.
How are things with the empress?
[CREW gasps]
An attack?!
Our forward Knightmare
unit is being wiped out!
Stop! All units, come to a halt!
[LELOUCH] Strange. We should
have had at least an hour
before we encountered
enemy forces.
Unless someone is guessing
our moves in advance.
[gasps]
A Knightmare?
Zoom in! Hurry!
[RAKSHATA]
Hm?
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
What is it?
Why's it equipped with the
same flight system we use?
[CREW gasps]
[KALLEN gasps]
[XING-KE]
Knightmare Frame Shen Hu.
And it's only running at
forty percent of full output.
How could the high
eunuchs have built it?!
[PILOT -A]
Flight Enabled or not,
it's only one unit! Surround it!
No, hold on!
[XING-KE] You underestimate
the Shen Hu at your peril.
[PILOT A grunts]
I'm caught!
[PILOT B grunting]
[XING-KE yells]
[CHIBA]
How dare you!
Hmph.
[XING-KE] Silence!
You people have no say here!
[CHIBA grunts]
[XING-KE]
Can you hear me, Zero?
[ZERO]
It can't be! Xing-ke?!
Zero! You shall not pass!
That's exactly why I'm calling:
I want to know why
we've stopped here.
[gasps]
Oh, I see.
Yes it's completely
soundproof in here. But...
[XING-KE]
Now, return the empress!
Do it and I spare your lives.
[KALLEN]
Xing-ke!
[XING-KE]
A flight-enabled Guren!
Kallen Kozuki!
[KALLEN growls]
[XING-KE] Even so,
the Shen Hu will crush you!
[TOHDOH]
Can we deploy the Zangetsu?
Well, we just detached
the float unit, so, uh...
[grunts]
[TAMAKI yells]
Get him, Kallen!
But... It isn't recharged.
Relax, buddy!
She fought off
the Knights of the Round before
with the guren just like this!
[KALLEN]
Scatter shot!
Not bad.
But I'm... a Black Knight Ace!
Show me, Shen Hu!
Show me your power!
Oh, no! That's...!
[ZERO]
You know what it is?
Well, you see...
He knows because
our team built it.
What are you saying?
[RAKSHATA] We developed it at
the same time as the Guren,
but it was too
high-spec to handle.
A one-of-a-kind Knightmare
that no pilot
could master. Until now.
[grunts]
[KALLEN]
Eat this!
[XING-KE]
Try this!
[EMPRESS gasps]
It's all right! We're going
to be all right!
The Heavenly
Particle Shocking Cannon.
It's just as powerful...
As powerful as the
radiant wave surger!
[ZERO] But how did our
enemies obtain it?
The Solidarity of Indian forces
might be split against us.
That old man, Maharaja!
[OHGI]
Does it have a weakness?
[RAKSHATA] It's based on
a different design concept
than the Guren.
There's no radiant wave system.
And piloting it takes skills
that are almost beyond human.
[OHGI] Well there's a human
piloting it now, isn't there!
[RAKSHATA]
Quite so.
[XING-KE] I have you!
Your fate is sealed!
That's right,
and so is yours.
What?!
[KALLEN] You can't get
away from me now.
And this is when
I take you apart!
[XING-KE] Really?
Then I have no choice.
I'm going to
have to crush you.
[KALLEN]
Let's see you try!
My power supply!
Kallen!
I said that she should
of recharged first!
[ASAHINA] The cockpit
block's wrapped up!
She can't eject!
We can cut the cables
with a pincer move!
Roger!
[gasps]
[XING-KE] I didn't choose
this course, you did.
I have only one objective...
To release the empress!
Release her at once!
[coughs] Dammit!
[XING-KE]
Now of all times?!
Can I fight like this? Huh?
[CHIBA]
What?!
[HINATA] Chinese Federation
behind us! A huge force!
Anti-aircraft barrage!
Cover Master Xing-ke!
[XING-KE]
Thank you Xiang-Lin!
[gasps]
No! Hold on a minute!
[ASAHINA gasps]
K-Kallen, no!
The Chinese Federation?
[LELOUCH] She's their
prisoner?! Impossible!
[ZERO] Kallen! Is your
radio working?!
[KALLEN]
S-Sorry I failed you.
[ZERO]
Forget about that!
[C.C. gasps]
[gasps]
[ZERO]
Don't give up!
I promise, I'll save you!
Am I clear?! No hasty moves!
Uh, right!
I understand. I won't give up!
I'll do what you--
[radio crackles]
[gasps]
Hurry, bring the Ikaruga
around immediately!
I respectfully
suggest we withdraw.
What?! We have to
get Kallen back!
Kallen Kozuki is a
single combat loss.
[OHGI gasps]
So, just leave her?!
[DIETHARD]
Mr. Minami, consider our choice.
You don't take on an enemy
like the Chinese Federation
over a single life,
no matter who it is.
We must preserve
our military strength
and hold out until we rendezvous
with the Indian forces.
Zero, it's your decision!
You gave special comfort
to Captain Kozuki before.
If you show her favoritism now,
it could put our entire
operation at risk.
It could ruin us.
[LELOUCH]
But...
You must put aside
your personal feelings.
Grand plans require sacrifice.
I'm waiting, Lelouch.
[beeping]
[gasps]
Uh, Knight of the Round.
[ZERO]
I've made my decision!
We're going in now!
But why?! If we lose,
we'll be crushed!
[ZERO]
If the Indians betray us,
we'll also be crushed.
Yes, but...
[gasps]
[ZERO] Chiba and Asahina,
use a crane wing formation!
We'll teach Xing-ke
the difference between
strategy and tactics!
Right! Yes sir.
Thank you, Zero!
We've been told to stand-by
here and wait for orders.
Oh. Say, Suzaku,
did you see these?
Show him those photos,
Lady Alstreim.
Uh, what are they?
[ANYA]
Here.
[SUZAKU] Oh, from my
welcome home party.
Ah. That one's an invasion
of privacy. Oh, Lelouch.
Huh? Lelouch?
If Shirley saw that,
she'd be really mad.
Uh huh.
Oh, that's right.
We have to contact Ashford,
but I need permission first.
[MILLY]
I see. Well, it can't be helped.
Lelouch and the others
must be so worried about us.
[ANYA]
Is this also Lelouch?
[ZERO] Black Knights!
Prepare for battle!
The terrain offers little cover
and there's no
geographic advantage.
[XING-KE] The enemy forces
is an improvised one.
Their chain of command
is all focused on Zero.
However, their Knightmare Frames
give them an advantage...
[ZERO] So the Chinese Federation
battle plan will be...
[XING-KE] To put the Shen
Hu on the front line and
break through...
[ZERO]
Our center!
[TOHDOH] I'll stop the
Shen Hu... with my Zangetsu!
Dragon Cavalry 3!
Our range is superior, so keep
firing as you advance!
[ZERO] We've blocked Xing-ke!
Akatsuki team, fire!
[HONG] It's true that
Xing-ke's pinned down,
but so is Tohdoh! Therefore...
The battle will be
decided by the skill
of the warriors!
[XING-KE]
Hit the enemy force head on
and hammer their
advance units!
Ignore their left
and right flanks!
Without Kozuki, we're one
move behind in this game!
They've broken
through our center!
Where's their main force?
[FUTABA]
On our forward line!
[ZERO] Right! All tasks
at hand are cleared!
Begin counterattack!
Chiba, right flank!
Asahina, left flank!
Use attack pattern sigma!
Prepare for rearward fire!
Focus barrage on main enemy
force! Hit the forward units!
Once the Shen Hu's
power's used up
and Xing-ke's neutralized,
the battle is ours.
[XING-KE]
Advance!
If we get bogged down here,
we'll be wiped out!
We're taking Kallen back!
Hit 'em hard!
Perpare fo hand-to-hand combat!
Draw swords!
There's more?!
You've deployed all your forces
to try and finish us, Zero?
Such wild risks!
His whole battle plan
hinges on the Shen Hu?
What a reckless daredevil!
[XIANG-LIN]
No.
He's drawing Zero into his net.
The true purpose of
this formation is...
[ZERO laughs]
Xing-ke,
your plan was to rip down
the bank of the waterway.
But I lowered the water
levels before the battle!
You think there isn't
enough to trap you.
That, Zero, is why you've lost.
Agh! What the...?!
[ZERO gasps]
[CHIBA]
I can't pull out!
Wait, isn't this...?
[XIANG-LIN]
Correct.
It's all reclaimed
irrigation land.
Even Zero didn't know
about the corruption
and shoddy construction.
The inferior materials
that would melt and
give way beneath their feet.
Xing-ke lead the way alone,
and then drew them back
into the position he wanted.
[LELOUCH]
He anticipated my moves!
He knew I'd
challenge him directly,
then deploy my forces in
this exact formation?!
[XING-KE] It is the
very land of our nation
that is giving us this victory!
Zero You've lost!
[ZERO]
Xing-ke!
[TOHDOH]
This battle is far from over!
Tohdoh the Miracle Maker!
Well done. But the enemy
main force is stopped!
All forces, advance!
Acknowledged!
[XING-KE] We'll take care of
their Knightmares later.
Concentrate fire on the
enemy ship's engine room!
Their barrier-shields
won't hold out forever!
Victory is at hand!
[LELOUCH] I've never been
out-maneuvered like this!
[gasps] What a disgrace!
Zero! I gave you my opinion.
I told you to withdraw!
[ZERO]
Then do it!
Protect the engine room
and pull back all forces!
Even if we return
to Horai Island...
[ZERO]
I know!
Ohgi, what about
the other place?
Uh! Right.
We finished a preliminary
recon and survey, but--
--[booming]
--[CREW gasps]
[ZERO] You've earned
your victory Xing-ke.
I should have killed you first.
You're as good a
tactician as I am
and as strong a
warrior as Suzaku.
One could say the heavens
blessed you twice.
Yes, but the heavens didn't
give him enough time to live.
[TOHDOH yells]
I have to hold on!
Just a little longer!
[HINATA] Bow-mounted
hadron scatter cannon, set!
[FUTABA]
Gefjun control synch, locked in!
[MINASE] Target lined up.
Ready to fire!
[ZERO] Right! Aim at
both enemy flanks!
Fire!
Impressive, Zero. So you
still had a hand to play.
Dragon Cavalry, spread out!
They're targeting battle groups!
[ZERO]
Tohdoh,
get the troops out of that
trap and back on solid ground.
The Ikaruga will lead
the enemy away!
Meet up with us at
rendezvous point 4!
I can't find any news reports
on the Chinese Federation.
Recovery of all remaining
Knightmares is now confirmed.
[RAKSHATA] I see. We're going
to be holing up in the
Mausoleum of
Eighty-Eight Emperors?
[DIETHARD] The enemy will
think twice about attacking us.
The greatest emperors from
Chinese history are buried here.
[C.C.] And they can only
approach us from straight on...
[OHGI] That way, we can fire the
bow-mounted hadron cannon.
[MINASE] Remember,
it's a single fire blast.
Now we just wait
for the Indian forces.
[CHIBA]
I doubt they're coming.
Besieged with no reinforcements.
[HINATA]
In that case,
there could have still
been room for negotiations.
[MINAMI] I never
believed the high eunuchs
would take that option.
[XING-KE grunts]
[ZHAO HAO] I thought
we told you not to move.
[CHENG ZHONG] Did you
really think we'd forgive you
after you plotted against us!
This is not the
time for revenge.
Or perhaps you don't really care
about rescuing the empress.
You've become obsolete.
We have more powerful
forces to serve us now.
We never anticipated
the Knights of the Round
getting into this fight.
You fools!
Bringing the forces of
a foreign empire
into our territory?
Aid from Britannia?
From the Avalon?!
Don't the high eunuchs know
who they're dealing with?!
Who do they think
conquered half of the E.U.!
It's Schneizel!
Second imperial prince.
[C.C.] Well, it seems
that the high eunuchs
are intent on wiping out
Xing-ke along with us.
[ZERO] Diethard, get our
little trick ready.
[DIETHARD]
What?! You mean here?
[ZERO]
Everything is in place.
And this will make a
most excellent stage.
[LELOUCH] I have
to strive for victory!
Even in this hopeless situation!
[REPORTER]
And we have a new report
from the Chinese Federation.
Taking advantage of
an attempted coup,
Zero appeared and kidnapped
the young Chinese empress.
Oh, really?!
You're okay then, madam Prez?!
[ALL gasp]
[MILLY] I'm with
Suzaku and the others.
What's the news saying there?
The TV and radio's just
talking about Zero now.
Thank God!
Madam Prez is alright!
[LELOUCH giggles]
And so it seems that Zero,
the empire's greatest enemy,
is about to meet his
end across the sea
in the Chinese Federation.
[LELOUCH] They've done it.
They've really done it.
Now, even if I use my
Geass on the empress
and make her my servant,
it'll be pointless!
The high eunuchs are
in complete control
and they're poised to
eliminate Xing-ke next.
In the end, we've been
cornered with no way out.
Even with Tohdoh
and the others here,
Suzaku is bound to join
the battle eventually.
There's almost no
chance for victory...
No, we're not finished yet!
I'll turn this tactical
battle upside down.
It's not going
to end here!
I won't let it!