[UNF ANNOUNCER]
99th emperor Lelouch,
who ascended the throne
only a few days ago,
has ordered the destruction
of the imperial mausoleum
which held the remains of
past Britannian emperors.
Following his abolition
of the aristocracy,
breaking up of
plutocratic cliques,
and liberation of the Numbers--
Odysseus and other
royals expressed support
for the new emperor
despite these actions.
However...
[TAMAKI]
He's just amazing!
[TOUDOU] Does he really
intend to completely
remake Britannia?
[RAKSHATA]
Don't you mean "destroy" it?
Are we to believe
Lelouch really did
hate Britannia, as he claimed?
He's eliminating any faction
which could oppose him.
Even in the U.F.N.,
most people are expressing
their support for
Emperor Lelouch.
[TAMAKI] I knew he was
really on our side;
I always said that!
[XIANG-LIN] Some media
people are calling him
the knight for justice
and hero of the masses.
Speaking of media,
where's Diethard at?
I doubt he's coming back here.
You're right. As long
as he's with Cornelia
and Schneizel,
he'll stay hidden.
So, what's our next move?
What do we do now?
What do you mean, from now?
Well, but I mean,
everything's different;
the new emperor is
doing good things.
He is?
[XING-KE]
No, he isn't.
[gasps]
[OHGI, VILLETTA]
Huh?
[TOHDOH]
It's the truth.
Emperor Lelouch has one--
no, Zero, has one goal.
Lelouch vi Britannia
commands each one of you!
Be my slaves! Now!
[MASKED SOLDIERS]
Yes, Your Majesty!
All hail Lelouch!
[LLOYD] Your Majesty,
won't you let me analyze
that power, just a little bit?
For science, of course.
[JEREMIAH]
Do you want to die, Lloyd?
You mean, in the
traditional sense?
Ridiculous.
Jeremiah Gottwald
returns from battle,
to announce that
he has vanquished
former Earl Rosenkreuz.
[LELOUCH]
Well done.
[JEREMIAH]
Hum.
Still, I'm not very
popular out there, am I?
The nobles are rising up
and rebelling everywhere,
isn't that true?
People resist when you take
away their vested intrests.
They fight back.
That's why we need to make them
fully understand how
foolish and pathetic it is
to cling to vain pedigrees
and past glories.
[LLOYD]
Is this a good thing?
[CECILE]
Is what a good thing?
[LLOYD groans]
Well, you know...
The way Prince Schneizel
and Princess Cornelia
have disappeared
without a trace.
This is the legitimate Holy
Britannian Empire, isn't it?
[CECILE]
Yes, you have a point.
And if they know what
Suzaku and the others
are actually trying
to do here...
[LLOYD] I wonder if we've
become cogs in a machine,
without even realizing it.
[CECILE]
By the way, did you know?
[LLOYD]
What?
[CECILE] Suzaku used to attend
school with his Majesty;
they had classes together.
Oh... Milly and Nina's school?
[MILLY]
I won't be back until night.
[NINA]
Covering something?
[MILLY]
A conference.
To decide if we support
His Majesty or Lelouch?
[MILLY]
That's part of it.
Area 11--sorry, I mean Japan--
It's about whether or not
we should go back
to the homeland
now that it's no longer
a part of Britannia.
And...?
[MILLY] Uh, well, even my family
isn't nobility any more.
Lelouch is the one who--
[MILLY]
Stop!
Uh?
Can we just drop
this whole subject now
and talk about something else?
Man, I'm hungry. Here, Nina.
[NINA]
Sorry, Rivalz.
[RIVALZ]
Forget it, forget it.
You shouldn't go out.
You're safe here in the school.
Thanks a lot.
When I built the F.L.E.I.J.A.,
I never in my
wildest dreams thought
all those countries would
target me. They're relentless.
[RIVALZ]
Mm...
[SUZAKU] So, soon after
ascending the throne,
the name Emperor Lelouch
has become part of history.
All because you dismantled
Britannian culture.
[LELOUCH]
The real work is yet to come.
At this moment, I'm about
to spill a sea of blood.
Enough blood to
wipe away all memory
of princess massacre forever
from peoples' minds.
Lelouch, are you saying...?
Euphy wasn't the only one.
It was Nunnally, too.
We've both lost so much.
Far, far too much.
But, to move forward
into the future,
we need to take over
the entire world.
[chuckles] Just saying those
words makes me laugh.
[C.C.] Yet you're both
absolutely determined
to do it, Isn't that right?
[LELOUCH] Yes. It's for the
sake of the Zero Requiem.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[LLOYD] Well then,
what will you do about
the problem at hand,
Your Majesty?
[LELOUCH]
Hm... I took over Britannia
to address that, but...
[C.C.] Is it true? About what
Schneizel is planning?
[LELOUCH] Yes. According to
the intelligence reports.
And, given that the
Toromo Agency in Cambodia
has seceded from Britannia.
When you add it all up...
It leads to one conclusion.
There's no choice...
We have to move the
plan to the next phase
before Schneizel has a chance
--to put his plan into action--
--[phone rings]
--Hm?
Yes, what is it?
[MAN ON PHONE] Majesty!
It's the Knights of the Round!
Huh?
[MAN ON PHONE]
They're approaching,
with the Knight of
One in the lead!
We can only confirm four
of the Rounds among them.
They're accompanied by
their personal forces!
[BISMARCK]
We swore absolute loyalty
to Charles zi Britannia!
We will never recognize
this damned usurper!
[alarm beeping]
[NONETTE] An interceptor?
But there's only one...
One is enough
with Lancelot Albion.
[gasps]
[NONETTE]
I can't track it!
He got me already?!
[BISMARCK]
Huh? The Albion?!
A ninth generation
Knightmare Frame!
It's Suzaku Kururu--
[GINO]
Will you wake up, Suzaku?!
You can still come back to us!
[SUZAKU] Come back?
You've got it all wrong.
If you've sworn true
loyalty to Britannia,
then it's you who should
join our side, Gino.
--[gasps]
--[SUZAKU] Or...
...will you stand
against Britannia?
Huh? Stand against it...?
[BISMARCK]
Suzaku Kururugi!
I heard that your
goal was to become
the Knight of One!
But I am the only Knight of One!
And I'll never lose that
title to a traitor like you!
My title is the Knight of Zero,
and that trumps you, Bismark.
An empty title with no honor!
We interrupt our programming
for this live broadcast from
the Holy Britannian Empire.
[KALLEN]
That's... the Lancelot!
[RAKSHATA]
With energy wings?
And it's challenging Bismarck.
How can he know
Lancelot's flight path?!
My Geass gives me the
power to see the future!
And again?!
Only once before
I used this power
when I battled Lady Marianne!
He can predict my
moves. But still...
Suzaku.
As we planned, this battle is
being broadcast to the world.
Right.
For the sake of the Zero
Requiem, I must be victorious!
And that's why I'm
ordering you, to live!
[SUZAKU]
Yes, Your Majesty!
[BISMARCK]
My name will always be linked
with the title of mightiest
knight of the empire!
Wh-What?!
What is this?
Is it the machine's
special functions...
...or is it Kururugi's skill?
[LELOUCH] Suzaku, your will
power is extraordinary.
Turning my Geass
command "to live"
into an unexpected weapon.
You've become a
warrior like no other.
Even though you can
predict my moves...
If I do this...!
Head on?! You insult me!
[gasps]
I failed you, Lady Marianne!
[gasps] The Knight
of One has fallen!
What have I become? Am I
a knight of Britannia?
And If I'm not then what am I
fighting these battles for?!
[LELOUCH]
To the people of the world!
[KALLEN]
Lelouch!
The video that you've
just seen is final proof
that I am the true
ruler of Britannia
in name and in deed.
Now that that is clear,
the Holy Britannian
Empire is ready
to join the United
Federation of Nations!
[ALL gasp]
Does that mean...
Britannia will be on our side?
There, ya see?
I told you he was one
of us. He's my buddy!
[LELOUCH]
For the negotiations, I will not
be with Suzaku Kururugi
nor any of my generals.
I shall follow all
rules of the U.F.N.
However, the site of
the negotiations shall be
the one nation which is neutral,
standing between Britannia
and the U.F.N. Japan.
The Ashford Academy
will be the site
of the conference.
[BOTH]
Wha--?
[RADIO GUY] This is one four
four. North wing, clear.
Is there something
going on, Schneizel?
A certain person decided
she didn't approve of us,
so she's chosen to flee.
[CORNELIA gasps]
We need to deploy Damocles
now. There's no more time.
Is that the only
option we have?
That will be up to
the world to decide.
[C.C.] Lelouch, are you
really certain about this?
Just me and a few
security police?
We're going there to
ask them for a favor.
To participate in an
enlightened democratic system.
Uh-huh.
And we know how everyone
loves their democracy.
[MILLY] We're coming to you
from Ashford Academy,
the site chosen by
His Majesty Lelouch,
Emperor of Britannia.
It is here that the U.F.N.
will debate whether to allow
the Britannian Empire
to become a member.
[MILLY] It's the emperor's
personal transport.
[CROWD murmuring]
Ooh!
Lelouch, is it really you?
[gasps] I'm sorry. Emperor
Lelouch has just landed
inside the school grounds.
[WOMAN] It's Lelouch,
the emperor for justice!
--[MAN] He's just a kid!
--[WOMAN 2] Your Majesty!
[RIVALZ] Lelouch! I need to
know the truth, Lelouch!
Why didn't you ever
tell me who you were?!
--[COP] Hey!
--[yelps]
--[COP] How dare you!
--[RIVALZ] Lemme go!
[COP]
Disrespecting the emperor!
We're friends!
He was my best friend
at school here. He was...
Lelouch!
Hey!
[COP]
Right...
[NINA] He's sorry! Let him go!
We'll leave right now!
[RIVALZ]
Huh?
Let's go. Come on.
[gasps]
Lelouch, tell me wh--
[LELOUCH]
Nice to meet you.
You're Capt. Kallen Kouzuki,
a leader of the Black
Knights, are you not?
That's right.
I'm here to escort you
safely to the conference.
Fine.
Do you mind if we take
the long way around?
[gasps]
I am feeling a bit
anxious about this.
A little walk might be helpful.
I understand.
[OHGI] Is Zero, uh, Lelouch--did
he come here to pull something?
[VILLETTA]
He can't.
The O.S.I.'s systems are
completely down now.
We've also supplied
the guards with goggles
that have special lenses.
Advanced Geass countermeasures.
Kouzuki wants us to
watch her closely;
if we think he used
his geass on her,
she wants us to shoot her.
She said to use the snipers.
You're all just paranoid.
He came here to make
friends; get over it.
Nostalgic, isn't it?
I'm... I'm grateful
for what you did.
[KALLEN] I know if it weren't
for you, I'd have ended my life
back in the Shinjuku ghetto.
The Black Knights would never
have existed at all. I was glad,
proud and honored to be needed
by our masked leader, Zero.
But, when I learned
you were Zero,
I didn't understand anymore.
Even so, the man I saw
fighting against Britannia...
Now you've joined
forces with Suzaku.
What are you really
trying to do?
[KALLEN]
Do you want personal power?
To be above everyone else?
Or is this just a game to you?
During the Black Rebellion,
Ohgi told me to guard
you with my life.
He told me that you could make
my brother's dream come true.
Lelouch, after everything
we've been through,
what do I mean to you?!
On the day that you left
the Ikaruga, you told me
"Kallen, you have to live."
This is it then. Bye, Lelouch.
The supreme council will be
meeting in the gymnasium.
So then, it is goodbye, Kallen.
[LELOUCH]
Chairman Kaguya Sumeragi
of the U.F.N. supreme council.
I desire that the Holy
Britannian Empire participates
in the United
Federation of Nations.
[KAGUYA]
Master Zero.
Do you understand
that participation
is dependent upon a
two third majority vote
of U.F.N. members?
Of course.
That's the democratic way
of doing things, right?
Yes, that's right.
[ASHFORD REPS murmuring]
This is rather uncourteous,
don't you agree?
It was former emperor, Charles,
who carried out all
those crimes, wasn't it?
[LELOUCH]
Geass countermeasures, huh?
Well, now it's clear that only
Kaguya and the core members
of the Black Knights
know about Geass.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
Now, what are you really
trying to do here,
treacherous Emperor Lelouch?
I'm surprised at you.
Isn't the new Britannia a better
country for the entire world?
[XING-KE]
That remains to be seen.
U.F.N. resolutions
are always determined
by majority vote.
Voting rights are apportioned
according to each member
nation's population.
[XING-KE] The Chinese Federation
has been broken up,
so the nation with the largest
population in the world now...
[OHGI]
...is Britannia.
[XIANG-LIN]
If we allow Britannia
to join the U.F.N. today...
[HONG GU] You will have
more than half the votes,
Emperor Lelouch.
In short, if we
vote in your favor,
you would usurp our power and
take control of the U.F.N.
So that's it! I always
knew he was a bad guy!
[RAKSHATA] He really is
exceptionally dim, isn't he?
[TAMAKI]
I heard that!
What's your response,
Emperor Lelouch?!
Break up your empire.
Let your territories
secede from Britannia...
...or limit your
total votes to 20%.
Those are your options.
Chairman Kaguya,
I have one question
that I would like to ask you.
You may do so.
[LELOUCH]
What trait is most important
for governing the world?
It's pride. The pride
of self-governance.
[LELOUCH]
Good answer.
[gasps]
You speak with
wisdom, Lady Kaguya.
However, I would submit
a different answer.
Oh, and what would
that answer be?
[LELOUCH]
The will to destroy.
Destroy?
Destroy the world
and even one's self!
Careful, he's trying
to pull something!
[gasps]
Dammit!
[ASHFORD REPS yelling]
[SUZAKU] I will not allow
this affront to His Majesty!
Where the hell were
our perimeter guards?!
[MAN ON RADIO 4] Sorry,
sir! He launched suddenly
from underwater!
Is he gonna make the
leaders of the entire world
obey him at gunpoint?
Deploy to Ashford Academy!
We need to save Lady Kaguya!
The Britannian forces
have started to move!
What's that?!
[MINASE] They're crossing
from international waters
into Japanese territory!
He's caught us off guard.
Meeting with the U.F.N.
and then choosing the
school as the site...
All of this was
nothing but a decoy!
If that's true, then
he's betrayed the trust
of the entire world.
You heard him.
He was never interested
in joinging the U.F.N.
In other words, his goal
is a pure dictatorship.
He abolished the
old aristocracy,
yet he still continues
to call himself emperor.
You're right.
Zero is-- Lelouch is now
the enemy of the world!
[XING-KE] Retreat!
Get out of there, Kozuki!
Negative, I'm taking
Lelouch down!
This Guren's the
only unit that can
go up against the Lancelot!
If you fight here,
you'll be putting
everyone's lives at risk.
There are leaders from
every nation on Earth!
But the Empress is
also in grave danger!
I know that, Kallen,
but the enemy is Lelouch!
He won't hesitate to kill
everyone around him!
You can't act on your own.
We have to let the
representatives decide
how to respond.
Otherwise, the U.F.N.
itself will collapse!
And that would leave
Britannia victorious!
[KAGUYA]
Suzaku...
[LELOUCH]
Now, Chairman Sumeragi...
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] I request
that you take the vote.
Will you allow Britannia
to join the U.F.N.?
We'd be voting under duress.
Will you stop them from
casting their decision?
No. Then let's start
the democratic process.
[RIVALZ] Lelouch and Suzaku!
What are they thinking?!
They've declared war
on the whole world.
[RIVALZ]
A roadblock?
Don't try to protect me,
it's not worth it.
You'll get tangled up
in this whole thing.
I'm not gonna let them
get their hands on you!
Why, just as a favor to
Milly?! If that's it--
Idiot! It's because
I'm your friend!
Ah?!
[breaks screech]
[LLOYD]
Congratulations!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[LLOYD laughing]
[MASKED SOLDIER] Priority
target one has been captured.
It all went as you
predicted, Your Majesty.
Good. Treat her with
courtesy as I instructed.
Oh, one more thing.
I'm sure there was
a student with her.
Let him go free.
[MASKED SOLDIER]
Yes, Your Majesty!
--[SUZAKU] Majesty!
--[LELOUCH] Hm?
[SUZAKU] Emergency dispatch
from the Avalon!
[LELOUCH]
What is it?
Pendragon, the capitol
city-- It's been...!
[LELOUCH]
Dammit! He struck first!
[CECILE] The radius of
destruction is approximately
100 kilometers.
We have to assume it was
caused by a F.L.E.I.J.A.
And that's not all...
There's a fortress
in the sky above it.
It's three kilometers long.
What's he doing now?
[SUZAKU] Lelouch! It's
just as you guessed!
[LELOUCH]
Yes, I had no doubt
that all the F.L.I.E.J.A.
warheads were there.
The sky fortress
Democles was developed
by the Toromo
Agency in Cambodia.
It is a perfect base
for the F.L.E.I.J.A.s.
Hm?
The only one who would know
the imperial private
channel is...
[grunts]
Do you enjoy forcing
others to submit
to your will, Lelouch?
What do you want?
I've gathered all the
F.L.E.I.J.A. warheads.
They're deployed
to the Damocles.
[LELOUCH]
You're prepared to attack
the Britannian emperor?
I'm afraid that's a moot point
since I don't recognize you
as the emperor, Lelouch.
I see.
I suppose you think that
you're best suited to rule.
No. You're mistaken.
There's another who's
destined for the throne.
Hm?
The one who's truly best suited
to rule Britannia is right here.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
Nunnally!
Listen well, Lelouch
and Suzaku, I declare...
You're my enemies from now on.
[LELOUCH] Nunnally, ever since
that day eight years ago
when we were abandoned,
I've needed a reason
to go on living.
Instinctively, I made
you my guiding star.
You became the
foundation of my life.
Perhaps, it is
about those issues
that Suzaku and Kallen
feel are so important.
Am I to once again lose the
very basis for my existence?
If not, do I now have to...!