[C.C.]
The actions one takes are
answered by consequences
waiting at their conclusion.
There are no exceptions,
and even Lelouch's power
cannot change this.
Despite his absolute ability
to make anyone obey him,
there is no escaping
the inevitable.
[C.C.] Lelouch has acted to
avenge his mother's death,
and to create a world where
his younger sister, Nunnally,
can find happiness.
[C.C.] Now he is confronted
by the results of his acts;
consequences he never imagined.
And there are more to come.
If these unintended consequences
help to create new worlds,
who will bear the blame for
the sins that are committed?
Who will take the punishment?
And who will measure it out?
[RADIO A]
Command to 4-0-1!
Move in to contain the enemy!
[RADIO B]
All Knightmare units!
Alpha-Niner, confirm status!
[RADIO C] Unit 9-0-3!
Alpha-Niner, confirmed!
[RADIO D] Enemy sighted,
bearing 7 o'clock!
Intercept now!
[RADIO B]
Underwater red leader...
No wait!
[DALTON]
Do not pursue!
Protecting the viceroy
has top priority!
[OHGI]
Zero! Come in!
Zero!
[C.C.]
Ohgi? Is that you? It's C.C.
Yes. How's Zero doing?
[C.C.] He's okay,
but he can't move now.
Order a retreat.
If we drag this out,
we'll be slaughtered.
Uh, yes. I understand. Got it.
[DIETHARD]
Hm?
[C.C.]
Is that what you wanted?
[LELOUCH]
Uh. Yes...
This is pathetic.
You're so shook up,
you can't even issue orders.
And Cornelia will--
Listen to me!
My handgun is missing!
Whoever has it now must
have taken it from me
when I was unconscious.
If that's true...
It means they saw your face.
There were at least two of them.
One who fired and
one who got shot...
Two.
[SHIRLEY sobbing]
[SOPHIE]
Shirley?
What are you doing
up so early?
Is that a letter?
I-It's uh...
Oh, it's nothing.
I bet it's a love letter, huh?
Something special for Lelouch?
[SHIRLEY gasps]
Mm... In a way...
[SUZAKU] You want to
meet Princess Euphemia?
To thank her!
I just wanted to thank her...
[MILLY]
She risked her life
to protect Nina during
the hotel hijacking!
She stood right up
and said, "I'm Euphemia!"
--Right?
--Really?
I want to meet her, too!
Why is that?
She's a real princess!
I could marry into royalty!
I'm sure that you
will never meet her
with such impure motives.
Impure?
[NINA gasps]
[RIVALZ] That's a little
harsh, isn't it, Nunnally?
You're on my side,
aren't you, Madame Pre--
Don't kiss up to me just because
Lelouch isn't hanging around.
Nunnally saw right
through you and so do I.
[NUNNALLY giggles]
Anyway, I'd like to meet
Princess Euphemia, too,
if I could.
[SUZAKU gasps]
[MILLY]
Huh?
Oh... What's the matter, Suzaku?
Uh... It's just she's a member
of the royal family and--
[phone rings]
[SUZAKU] Hello, Ashford
Academy student council.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku?
Lelouch?
[NUNNALLY gasps]
[LELOUCH] Is there...
anything unusual there?
Yeah, there is...
[LELOUCH gasps]
You're not here.
[LELOUCH]
Oh, right...
[SUZAKU] Shirley didn't
show up either, by the way.
[SUZAKU]
You know, Lelouch,
you've been cutting
classes lately.
You need to take school
more seriously!
[LELOUCH]
Right, "Mister honor student."
Can you give
Nunnally a message?
Tell her I'll be late tonight?
Did you say "tonight"?
More like every night.
What's the point in going to the
same school if I never see you?
[ARTHUR meows]
[SUZAKU screams]
[LELOUCH]
Hm? What's going on?
[SUZAKU]
Uh, nothing!
Uh... Hey! Arthur! Ar-- Ow!
--[clicks]
--[dial tone]
[LELOUCH] I wonder what's
going on over there? Hm.
[C.C.]
So then it seems like--
Right. It appears he
doesn't know about me.
That eliminates one group--
The military.
[C.C.] Aside from them
and the Black Knights,
I can't think of anyone else
who would have been there.
[LELOUCH] Someone from
the Japan Liberation Front
could have survived.
And they only stole your gun?
I think I'll have Ohgi check
out the black market then.
And the blood?
It'll take time to analyze.
There's something else...
I thought I saw Shirley there.
[C.C.]
Oh, the girl who kissed you?
[LELOUCH grunts]
Give it a rest, will ya?!
[C.C.] Just making sure I got
the right girl, lover boy.
But if she was there,
then there's something
we need to know, and we
better find out fast.
[DALTON] In this last
operation and also at Narita,
they were specifically
targeting you, Your Highness.
Eliminating the leader's
a standard tactic.
[GUILFORD] They also
eliminated Prince Clovis.
Zero is not merely
fighting Britannia...
He has a deep hatred
for the royal family,
and he wants blood.
Hatred?
[ZERO]
Euphemia...
You were willing to sacrifice
You haven't changed.
[CORNELIA]
Careful, Euphy.
[EUPHEMIA]
Huh?
[CORNELIA] I don't want another
crisis like at the hotel.
[GUILFORD]
Why not assign a knight to her?
A knight?
Yes. If we assign one knight
as a permanent sentinel,
then we can build a complete
royal guard unit around him.
As sub-viceroy,
Princess Euphemia has the
right to a personal champion.
[CECILE] This thing about
"saving people's lives,"
at first I thought he was
just, y'know, sensitive,
but now, I mean it's more
like an obsession, isn't it?
[LLOYD] His performance
data is still solid, right?
Is this a good time to put that
new thing to a test with him?
But we're still fine-tuning.
What I'm saying is, treating
Suzaku like he's just another
part of the machine could
have serious consequences.
We better deal with the
human issue here first.
Pardon me, but really,
aren't you taking care of him
in place of someone else?
[CECILE gasps]
I'm not sure about that, but...
[LLOYD]
Hm?
[CECILE] You're quick to
catch on to something silly,
--aren't you?
--[LLOYD chuckling]
I'm the boss so
you're stuck with me!
Hey, what are you doing
out here by yourself?
I'm waiting.
I need to wait till they
finish disinfecting my room.
[C.C.]
Why should I have to go rifling
through some girl's underwear?
This is going to cost you!
[LELOUCH]
It always does.
[C.C.]
Hmph!
You could do this solo,
and she'd be thrilled to know
the man she loves went
searching through--
[LELOUCH]
That's my business.
[C.C.] Once again, making
a big deal out of nothing.
Well, there's no sign
of that gun in here.
And her diary only
goes up to the 14th.
[LELOUCH]
Fourteenth?
[C.C.]
Yeah.
But that's the day that
her father had died.
[gasps]
What?
They're a bunch
of photos of you.
[LELOUCH]
Of me?
[C.C.] How could our
suspect be so sweet?
Ah, just can the
sarcasm, would ya?
[LELOUCH]
Narita?
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu, how could you do this?
[MAO]
Yes, how could he?
[SHIRLEY gasps]
A fine very memorial.
Isn't that right,
Miss Shirley Fenette?
[SHIRLEY]
Wh-Who...?
[TAMAKI] Man, it was so close!
We had her right there!
[KALLEN] Next time, I'll
beat that white Knightmare.
[MINAMI]
Aw, don't sweat it.
Yeah, Tamaki got thrashed
in the first minute.
[GROUP laughs]
The JLF war ship...
[KALLEN]
Huh?
[OHGI]
Why'd it blow up?
It self-destructed.
We did contact them and
say we would help, right?
Yo, that's why Zero took action.
I know! They wanted
to see his face!
[laughs]
You're not doubting
Zero again, are you?
Well, it's just that--
[DIETHARD]
Yes...
It's just that the timing
was too convenient, right?
So what are you going to do if
you find out Zero was behind it?
What are you trying to say?!
Yeah, Diethard!
I heard you got
wussy and ran away!
A gutless Brit's
got a lot of kahunas
talking trash to his
superiors like that!
I was making an assessment;
that's my new job here.
Ohgi, you agreed to
it, too, didn't you?
--[KALLEN] Huh?
--[OHGI] Uh...
That's right.
And Zero did approve it.
[C.C.]
So, do you love her?
This girl called, "Shirley"?
[LELOUCH]
Don't know.
[C.C.]
Do you hate her?
[LELOUCH]
Don't know.
Then why are we
going to Narita?
You know the reason why.
'Cause she may have
discovered who I am.
[C.C.]
What if she really does know?
Are you going to kill her?
[LELOUCH gasps]
If you have someone
you don't want to lose,
you should keep
them at a distance.
So is that... from experience?
No. It's a way of life.
[MAO]
He's a cruel man, isn't he?
Lelouch?
[SHIRLEY]
H-How do you know about Lulu?
[MAO]
Aw, he deceived you.
Never told you he's Zero.
[SHIRLEY gasps]
Who are you?! What do you want?!
[MAO] The same mouth that
ordered your father's death
stole a kiss from
your tender lips.
He's a very bad man,
and you like it!
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[MAO]
Punishment must be measured out.
To him...
...and to you.
To me?
[MAO]
I know everything.
All that happened that night...
[SHIRLEY panting]
[VILETTA]
Is that Zero?!
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[VILETTA]
Well, well, what a shocker.
The student is Zero himself!
A Britannian.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
When I bring him to
Viceroy Cornelia,
she'll make me a noble--
not just a Knight of
Honor, real nobility!
And he's still alive, too!
What kind of grand execution
will they have in store for him?
Of course, you'll
be rewarded, too.
--[gasps]
--[SHIRLEY whimpering]
Stupid of me! He's your
boyfriend, isn't he?!
--[SHIRLEY] Lulu!
--[gunshot]
[MAO]
So you're a killer, too.
Just like Zero.
[SHIRLEY gasps]
No! That's not true, I just--
And you actually used
your father's death
for your own gain!
[SHIRLEY gasps]
No! I just... I just...!
Cunning little woman!
You knew he'd feel sorry
for you, didn't you?
So you played it for
all it was worth.
No! You're wrong!
[MAO] Did his sympathy
make you all tingly?
Stop it!
[MAO] Playing the
tragic heroine again?
No! I'm not doing that!
[MAO] A girl who kills and then
goes fishing for attention?
Only evil witches do that.
I didn't-- I never meant--
You knew there was another
girl who liked Lelouch,
and you wanted to get
him away from her.
[SHIRLEY gasps]
Now you have to pay
the price, Shirley.
[SHIRLEY sobs]
[MAO] Do you want to carry
these feelings around
for the rest of your life?
All by yourself?
Unless you atone and
completely free your heart,
you and Lelouch will
both be lost in your sins.
Forever.
[LELOUCH sighs]
I thought she'd be here.
[C.C.] We'll have to split
up and look for her.
[LELOUCH] Do you even know
what Shirley looks like?
[C.C.]
What's with you now?
[LELOUCH] The chance is so
slim, I doubt she's even here.
What if she really does know?
Are you going to kill her?
[LELOUCH] No, wait.
There was someone else here.
Where'd they go?
And what were they
doing with Shirley?
Calm down.
--Work from the beginning.
--[phone rings]
--[gasps]
--[ringing continues]
It's Shirley!
I'm here.
Where're you calling from?
[MAO chuckles]
Where indeed?
[LELOUCH]
Who are you?!
You scum!
What have you done
with Shirley?!
Ooh, I like it! The scary face!
The face of a man whose
woman was stolen away!
What the hell did
you do with her?!
You want to know?
Then you'll have to
accept my challenge.
You specialize in this.
Don't you?
[C.C.] Are you familiar
with Balinese art?
I don't have a photo, but I can
paint her in Batuan style.
What, I'm supposed to wait
around here while you do that?
I don't think so.
Why don't you go ask the
police or the soldiers?
I'd like to avoid that
kind of dull crisis.
Then why don't you climb up on
something tall and look around?
Very well, nevermind.
[C.C.]
Hm?
What's Lelouch up to?
Huh?
[C.C.]
It can't be! Mao!
[LELOUCH]
Is he the one?
Our other eye-witness?
I'm sure this chess
game is just a ploy.
[LELOUCH] His real goal is to
lure me to an isolated place.
You know, I've never actually
played this game
before, don't you?
[LELOUCH] Calling on my mobile,
was he just being theatrical?
No... He didn't know
what I look like!
That means he didn't
see me that night,
and he didn't have time
to find a photo of me.
He hasn't planned this out.
He's wingin' it. Which means--
There's an opening you can use?
[LELOUCH gasps]
[MAO] Shouldn't you be thinking
about the game a bit more?
You could lose.
[LELOUCH grunts]
You liar, you have
played this game before!
[C.C.]
Lelouch, even you...
No, because it's you,
you can never beat Mao!
[LELOUCH grunting]
[LELOUCH]
Impossible.
He's got me trapped?!
[MAO chuckles]
So, can we just call it my game?
Hm?
[LELOUCH] How could he
predict every move I made?!
Who is this guy?!
[MAO]
Didn't C.C. tell you about me?
[LELOUCH gasps]
Well done!
In one lightning moment,
you came up with 14
possible identities for me.
And one of them is
precisely correct.
[LELOUCH gasps]
He has Geass, too!
Let's see now, for your Geass,
you have to look directly
into someone's eyes.
Oh, I know all of the rules
for your little gift.
You can read minds!
You could call my Geass
"mind reading."
What the hell did
you do to Shirley?!
Tell me! What did
you do, kill her?!
Of course not.
[LELOUCH gasps]
It's Shirley!
So now then, let the vital
punishment games begin.
[OHGI]
Zero...
You weren't yourself yesterday.
Why do I have this feeling?
[OHGI gasps]
[OHGI]
Are you all right?!
Talk to me!
Hey!
C'mon!
[VILETTA groans]
You're alive!
So... it's you...! Zero!
[OHGI gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Shirley, that gun is...
Yes. It's Zero's.
Your gun, Lulu.
[LELOUCH grunts]
[MAO]
Why don't you use your Geass?
[LELOUCH gasps]
[MAO] I'm pretty sure you
haven't used it on her, right?
[LELOUCH growls]
[MAO] Of course if you do,
I'll just shoot you, myself.
[gun cocks]
[LELOUCH]
Can he read any thoughts?
Or only those on the surface?
Are there conditions
to his Geass?
A time lag? Time limit?
And what's he after?!
If he plans to kill me, then...
Keep thinking about it.
That's your strong-point, right?
Thoughts spinning round
and round and round--
[LELOUCH]
Shut up!
This is a fitting death, poetic
justice for a thief like you.
[LELOUCH]
Huh...?
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu, die.
[LELOUCH gasps]
We'll atone for our sins.
We have to!
I'll die with you!
W-What?
She's already killed one time.
She shot the person
who saw your face.
All to protect
your little secret.
Then, that blood was...
It's time to end
this together, Lulu.
Yes, yes, sinners
must be punished.
You put her up to all of this!
[LELOUCH]
I see. He reads her mind,
and then it's easy for him
to confuse and control her.
Yes! That's right!
No, don't let him trick you!
Shirley, he's just--
Come now, are you
actually saying this?
The guy who lied to
her from the start?
No! Stop it!
If murder's a sin, then this
absolutely increases the sin!
Oh, I like the rhetoric!
Very pithy!
Shirley, did you
really kill somebody?!
And if you did kill, was he the
one who was controlling you?!
Shirley pulled the
trigger and she knows it.
When you hide away your
sins, it only get worse.
He's trying to
confuse you, Shirley!
Why don't you just shut up?!
[LELOUCH groans]
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[SHIRLEY sobs]
[MAO]
What are you hesitating for?
He's the one who
killed your father!
Don't you know he's
a sinner? Kill him now!
[SHIRLEY]
But...
[LELOUCH]
Shirley!
[SHIRLEY]
I just... I don't...
What the heck's
up with this girl?
Her thoughts are
just a jumble now.
I'll just have to do it--
[SHIRLEY]
Stop it!
Just stop it!
Fine, consider it stopped.
You two just do
whatever it is you want.
[SHIRLEY sighs]
Shirley!
[LELOUCH grunts]
What a pain.
It was so dramatic and juicy...
Now I'll have kill them
the old boring way--
[grunts]
Who did that?! Why didn't
I sense them there?!
It couldn't be--
C.C.!
I just knew it!
We finally meet again!
It's you! It's really you!
[C.C.]
Are you awake, Mao?
Forgive me, Mao.
Thank the way.
See, Mao? You can do it!
Thank you, Mao.
[MAO laughs] You look beautiful,
C.C.! I love that new look.
C.C.! I'll come to see
you as soon as I can!
I promise. I promise!
[C.C.]
Mao...
I never thought you would
come out among people.
[LELOUCH]
It's all right now.
It's over.
Lulu, I really
did kill someone.
That's why I...
[LELOUCH]
It's because of me.
It's not your fault.
And I shot you with your gun.
I'm still alive.
But... I did it!
[LELOUCH] Shirley, any sin
you committed is mine to bear.
[SHIRLEY]
I wanted you to be kind to me...
[LELOUCH]
What's wrong with that?
[SHIRLEY]
Even though my father died...
[LELOUCH]
Don't worry, it's time to forget
all the bad things that
have happened to you.
[SHIRLEY]
I can't!
Yes, you can!
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[LELOUCH] I'll help
you forget all of this.
Impossible.
[LELOUCH] Shirley, I'm
sorry about your father.
If I could be reborn into
a new life... I would.
Lulu... No, don't!
Oh, hello.
Um, did you lose someone
in your family, too?
No, not someone
from my family.
It was a friend.
Someone, well, very...
important.
I understand.
But I didn't know...
I didn't know until
after I lost her.
Then I realized how
much she meant to me.
How her smile saved me.
And how I'll never be
able to argue or laugh
with her like that again.
[SHIRLEY] I see.
You loved her, didn't you?
You must feel terrible.
Right now, I don't know anymore.
Well, the morning
always comes again.
What?
I have to say, it's funny.
I know that I came out
here for some reason,
but I can't remember
exactly what it was now.
Maybe it's because I already
put the whole thing behind me,
something I wanted to let go of.
Maybe it was something I
thought I couldn't forget.
Maybe I was full of sadness.
But morning still comes, right?
That's why you shouldn't try to
hold back your
thoughts like that.
Yes, you're right.
I feel the same way now.
Thanks a lot...
...for everything.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
[LELOUCH]
Maybe I was too soft.
Maybe it would have been
better to just kill Shirley.
But...
Geass, the power of the king,
will condemn you to
a life of solitude.
So I need to harden
my heart even more.
Then, it's me and Mao.
Payback!