[theme music]
-Quiet, Matsuda.
This is not the time
to be fooling around.
Knock it off.
-Yes, sir.
-This is the Kira investigation.
Stop messing around!
-Sorry, Aizawa.
[shout]
MALE SPEAKER: Matsuda,
please don't, Matsuda.
-After all, the last thing
I want is to be dead weight.
-Ryuzaki, is there
anything I can
do to help with
the investigation,
besides the manager thing?
-Could you get me
another cup of coffee?
[gasp]
[laughing]
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER):
I want to help, too.
I want to contribute
to the case.
-I love you.
So please, don't tell me
you're going home now.
Instead, say you'll
stay by my side.
-Uh, Mr. Director,
I can't do this.
I have a boyfriend.
Can we cut the love
scenes, please?
-Uh--
-Wait.
Where'd this come
from all of a sudden?
-Can't we just fake
kiss or something?
DIRECTOR: What?
You're kidding.
You can't expect us to
make a movie like that.
MISA: If I say no, then it's no.
OK?
DIRECTOR: Come on!
FEMALE SPEAKER: Come on.
Get rid of her.
Fire her.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER): The Yotsuba
Group's main Tokyo office.
And today is Friday.
-All the death that are
beneficial for Yotsuba
are concentrated
around the weekends.
-Hmm.
-The last thing I want
to be is dead weight.
-Mogi's been incredibly
efficient from the start.
-Quiet, Matsuda!
This is not the time
to be fooling around.
-Would you cut it out?
-That is his specialty.
-And could you get me
another cup of coffee?
-Matsuda!
[grunt]
MISA: Matsu!
Hello, Matsu, get over here.
-I guess he had to
run off somewhere.
-(DISAPPOINTED) Oh.
-Hmm.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: All right.
For the time being,
I want you to start
going over this list here.
-Yes, sir.
Right away.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Would I
punish evildoers and criminals
if I could kill by just
seeing a name and face?
Is that what I'd do if I
had that sort of power?
I mean, it's true
that there are lots
of people around that the
world could frankly do without,
but I don't think I'd
become a murderer just
to change the world.
-Huh?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Surely
I wouldn't do that.
No, I'm thinking
too hard about this.
There's no way anyone
could murder so many people
and not have any memory of it.
L: What's wrong?
You've been staring at me
for the last two minutes.
Wait, let me guess.
You must be annoyed
because I'm the only one
eating cake at the moment.
Am I right?
-Uh, no, that's not it.
-Here.
-Really, don't worry about it.
[beep]
-Hmm?
WATARI (ON COMPUTER): Ryuzaki.
L: Yes, what is it?
WATARI (ON COMPUTER):
Detective Eraldo Coil has just
received a private request
to investigate and reveal
the identity of L.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI:
Isn't Eraldo Coil
supposed to be the
second-greatest detective
in the world after L himself?
Who on earth would
send such a request?
WATARI (ON COMPUTER):
The man who sought out
Coil's services is Masahiko
Kida, the head of the Rights
and Planning Department
of the Yotsuba Group's
headquarters in Tokyo.
-So it is Yotsuba.
-We know that Yotsuba
must be linked to Kira.
If they're trying to
find out L's identity,
it's probably because they
want to kill him and need
that information to do it.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI:
This isn't good.
We're already short-handed
enough as it is,
and now we have to
worry about Coil, too.
-Mm, mm.
It's quite all right.
The detective known
as Eraldo Coil is me.
-Oh?
L: It's quite simple, really.
Three of the greatest detectives
in the world, L, Coil,
and Deneuve, they're
all actually me.
It's been my
experience that people
who try to find me
usually fall for this.
I'll give you this strawberry
if you keep it a secret, OK?
-Mm.
-I'm impressed as
always, Ryuzaki.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER):
Maybe I should
leave while I still
have a chance.
No, then there would have
been no point in coming here.
Or should I wait
until everyone's gone
and search their offices?
I-- I can't.
I'd probably get
caught doing that,
and then-- maybe I
should get out of here.
SHIMURA: [grumbling]
Not this again.
-Huh?
-I'm too tired.
-Look on the bright side.
At least it falls
on the weekend.
We never know how long
these confidential meetings
will go on far.
Can you imagine if we
did this on Mondays?
That would be the worst
start to the week.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER):
Confidential meetings?
All right!
Ah.
The 19th floor.
I've made it this far.
I'm going to see it through.
-All right.
I just have to get
close to him, right?
Leave it to me.
-And you want me to
make sure that we're
able to breach the security
and override the surveillance
cameras in the Yosuba
Group's head office.
Is that all?
-Yes.
At this point,
it's safe to assume
that Kira and the Yotsuba Group
are connected in some way.
We're going to investigate
Yotsuba to determine
who holds Kira's
power and if there
is more than one person
who possesses this ability.
We need a clear
understanding, quickly.
-Hmm?
Mm.
-We cannot let anyone from
Yotsuba figure out that we are
investigating them.
Please realize that
if they do notice,
it means we won't be
able to catch Kira.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER): Damn it,
I can't hear them clearly.
If only I could hear just one
thing, something important.
[executives murmuring]
EXECUTIVE: Kill him.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER): I just
heard someone say kill!
EXECUTIVE: I'm sure
Kira would approve.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER): Kira!
There it is.
Kira, they said it!
What's that?
Let's have Kira get rid of him?
I heard it!
They really are
working with him.
I did it!
This is huge!
[grunting]
-Who the hell are you?
L: Please be sure not
to act impulsively out
of panic or haste.
And don't take matters
into your own hands.
[beep]
WATARI (ON COMPUTER): Ryuzaki.
L: Yes, what is it?
WATARI (ON COMPUTER):
I have just
received an emergency
signal from Matsuda's belt.
-Oh, where is he?
-It seems that it's coming
from within the head
office of the Yotsuba Group.
-Uh, sorry to
barge in like this.
Um, my name is Taro Matsui.
I'm an agent with
Yoshida Productions.
I just dropped by to ask
if your company would
be interested in using our
top multitalented start, Misa
Amane, as your new spokesperson.
[nervous laugh]
-Hmm.
-Disregard everything
I just said.
We'll need to
rethink our strategy.
[sigh] Matsuda, you idiot.
HATORI: Yoshida
Productions, Taro Matsui.
He doesn't have anything
suspicious on him.
I suppose that means he
isn't a corporate spy.
-[laughing] Right.
Um, so please take Misa-Misa
into consideration.
(VOICEOVER) THese two were
only acting as guards.
The rest of them
must be discussing
how they'll get rid of me.
Oh, there's no way out of this!
I'm going to killed for sure.
I wonder if the emergency
signal got through.
Never mind that.
Even if it did, will
Ryuzaki come and save me?
Oh no, what's going to happen?
[ringtone - "alumina"]
-Go ahead.
You can answer it.
Don't say that
you're here, though.
And hold it away from your ear.
Make sure we can listen
in on the conversation.
-OK.
Hello?
L (ON PHONE): Yo, Matsui!
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER): Ryuzaki.
Oh.
L (ON PHONE): Uh,
it's me, Asahi.
It's been a while, buddy.
-Asahi!
Yeah, it's been a long time.
-Ha, it doesn't sound
like you're out right now.
Don't tell me
you're home already.
MATSUDA (ON PHONE): Yeah.
-So, you by yourself?
-Yeah, I'm by myself.
What's up?
-He's not with Misa
Amane right now.
Matsuda must be on his own.
-Hmm.
-So, do you want to, like,
go out drinking tonight?
MATSUDA (ON PHONE): Huh?
Right now?
Oh, sorry, I'll have
to pass tonight.
-Ah, what's the matter?
Don't tell me your wallet
is in trouble again.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER): In trouble.
-Yeah, that's right,
big troubles with money.
You know me way too
well. [laughing]
-Matsuda's saying
he's in big trouble.
-Oh, that's too bad.
Guess I'll drag you out
some other time, all right?
See you, buddy.
[beep]
-Uh.
A-anyway, what do you think
about contracting Misa-Misa?
I think she'd be great
spokesperson for your company.
-Hmm.
If you're going to promote
one of your clients,
shouldn't you at least
bring them with you?
-Do you expect us to believe
your this girl's manager?
-Well, to be honest,
at the moment,
she's filming a movie nearby.
Once she's finished, I'll call
her and get her over here.
Then you can see why she'd
make a great spokesperson.
(VOICEOVER) I have to keep
stalling them somehow.
-Misa's cell phone is
on voicemail right now.
I left her a
message and told her
to get back to me
as soon as she can.
-What are you planning
to do, Ryuzaki?
-Well, we have to consider
that if Matsuda dies,
our suspicions about the Yotsuba
Group would be confirmed.
-Hmm.
L: Let's just watch the
situation for the time being.
-What should we do?
-The main question is
whether he heard anything.
-If it's a possibility,
no matter how small,
we'll have to kill him.
-I'm wondering if he
really did come here just
to promote his client.
He could be an undercover cop.
-No, that can't be it.
The Japanese police
have completely
withdrawn support
from the Kira case.
-Look, it doesn't
really matter who he is.
We have no choice
but to kill him.
-Hmm.
You know, now that
I think about it,
it might be good to have her
as the face of our company.
-Hmm?
-Ah, exactly.
Her shoot should be done
soon, so please wait.
She'll convince you.
-Mm, I'm beat.
[sigh] [gasp] I got
a call from Light!
He really does worry
about me when I'm late.
[laughing]
[phone ringing]
-M-Misa?
MISA (ON PHONE): Light!
I'm sorry I've been
working so much.
I'll be finished soon, 'kay?
-Misa, you're not with Matsuda
at the moment, are you?
-Him?
He's a total jerk.
He just ran off
and left me here.
[phone ringing]
Oh.
Hang on.
I'm getting a call
on my work phone.
Oh hey, it's from Matsu.
-Misa's just received
a call from Matsuda.
-Tell her to hold her phone so
that we can listen in as well.
MATSUDA (ON PHONE): Misa-Misa,
when you're finished filming,
come over to the Yotsuba
Group head office.
It's still tentative,
but there's
a chance you may
be able to appear
in Yotsuba's commercials.
We're working it out now.
-(EXCITED) What?
Are you for real?
You're amazing, Matsu!
So that's what you've
been up to all this time!
Don't worry.
We're wrapping up soon.
MATSUDA (ON PHONE): Great.
It's just a short trip by taxi.
-Huh?
-Listen to me, Light.
There is a chance that we
may be able to save Matsuda,
but we won't be able to
do it without Misa's help.
She'll listen to you and do
anything you say, won't she?
-Uh--
-I'm Misa-Misa.
My only rule is
I don't do nudes,
but swimsuits and
lingerie are totally OK.
It's really nice to meet you.
[nervous laughter]
-Hmm.
I gotta admit, she is
really cute in person.
-That's not exactly the main
issue now, wouldn't you agree?
-By the way, Matsu, since
Yotsuba's a big catch,
I got the OK from our office
to have a special reception.
-Hmm?
Reception?
[giggling]
MODELS: Good evening.
We're very pleased to meet you.
-Tonight, I'll be entertaining
you as our special guest,
along with the girls
from the agency.
-Hey, is it just me, or
is this getting weird?
-Hmm.
-Well, it can't be helped.
Right now, we can't afford
to leave Misa's manager
alone for a second.
-Let's just go with it.
I'm going to enjoy myself.
EXECUTIVE (MURMURING):
All right.
Hard to go wrong with this.
Hmm.
[nervous laughter]
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER):
Ryuzaki and the others
will be able to
watch us from here.
This is my way out.
-Here you are.
Drink right up. [laughing]
-Man, we gotta do
this more often.
-Hmm.
Well, well.
Misa's pretty good at
this sort of thing.
--[shaky laughter] [sigh]
(SLURRED) Excuse me, guys.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Hmm.
Ryuzaki, are you watching this?
-Yes.
-L-look, I'm really
sorry that I--
-That's not important right now.
MATSUDA (ON PHONE): OK.
Listen, the eight
men who came here
were having a
meeting to determine
who they'd get Kira
to kill for them.
-Oh?
[grunt]
-I heard them say it clearly.
There's no doubt
they're behind this.
-Yes, that is probably true.
But if you did overhear
them, and they caught you,
then they'll almost certainly
be trying to kill you now.
-I know.
Do you think there's anything
I can do to save myself?
L (ON PHONE): Well,
luckily, you're still alive,
so we may be able to save you.
But for that to
happen, you will have
to die before they can kill you.
-What?
L (ON PHONE): I want you to
listen to me very carefully.
MATSUDA: [gasp] No way.
But that's-- that's crazy.
[murmuring]
-And you know our
company is expanding.
-Hey!
-What the hell?
EXECUTIVE (MUTTERING):
Who's that?
-(DRUNKENLY) Wow, I am so drunk.
[uneasy murmuring]
-Huh?
-Oh, h-hi, everyone.
Everyone having fun?
Good.
That's great.
Now, everyone, the
moment you've all
been waiting for,
the Taro Matsui show!
[laughing]
-Hey, what are you doing/
-Yay!
You can do it!
Go Matsu!
-All right, here we go.
Uh--
-Hey, you're drunk.
That's way too dangerous.
-Don't worry.
I'm just fine.
I do this all the time.
[grunting]
[astonished shouting]
TAKAHASHI: What the
hell are you doing?
Get in here!
-Stop!
Are you crazy, you idiot?
-It's all right.
(STRAINING) No prob.
[shouting]
[screaming]
-He fell!
This can't be good.
-(SHOUTING) Ah, no!
I heard a thud, so I came out.
This is just horrible.
Someone call an ambulance!
MATSUDA: Geez. this
sure is a crappy role.
-Look, everyone, I think
you should all just
leave this for us to
take care of and go home.
-What?
But--
-Don't worry.
We'll handle it.
Just don't forget about me
for your next campaign, OK?
-Let's go.
If the press sees
us, we're in trouble.
[siren]
EXECUTIVE: Yeah.
FEMALE SPEAKER: What's going on?
Did someone jump?
-Well, we're lucky that he ended
up dying right in front of us,
at any rate.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-Mm.
-While I'm aware of the fact
that we're short-handed,
I'm not very pleased about
having to do this sort of thing
myself.
Matsuda, you idiot.
[sigh]
-"Misa Amane's
manager dies in fall."
Hmm.
[phone ringing]
Yes.
AIBER (ON PHONE): You're
Masahiko Kida, VP of the Rights
and Planning Department
at Yotsuba's Tokyo office,
correct?
-Yes, that's right.
And who am I speaking to?
-I go by the name Eraldo Coil.
I'm calling to discuss
my terms with you.
EXECUTIVE: What?
A $2 million advance and
$8 million upon completion?
Is he out of his mind?
-That's not all.
Even if we don't commission him,
we have to pay him $2 million
just to keep him silent.
-So he wants hush money, huh?
-If he's saying
something like that,
we should assume Coil
knows quite a bit already.
-This it's getting ridiculous.
I've had it.
I want out of these
meetings right now.
I don't know who Kira
is, and I don't care.
I just don't want to get wrapped
up in this and end up in jail!
HIGUCHI: No.
-Huh?
HIGUCHI: Hatori, I think you are
going to end up dead tomorrow.
-No, wait.
I was only joking.
It's not like that.
I'm in.
I'll see this to the end.
-So what are we going to do?
Coil is still willing
to accept the job,
despite what he already knows.
-Isn't it obvious?
He'll become partners with
us, as long as we pay him.
-His demand are
exorbitant, but we
need to have someone as
skilled as Coil on our side.
-Good point.
Pay him.
It doesn't matter how much.
-Exactly.
We'll just have to pay him.
Uh--
-All right, we'll contract Coil.
Anyone have any objections?
-(TOGETHER) No objections.
WEDY: L, are you listening?
(SCOFFING) I am To disappointed.
I thought this would
be a challenge.
Security level here is a joke.
They've left it all to
a single contractor.
There weren't even
any wiretap detectors.
It's been about a week since
I first snuck into the place.
It looks like things have
been moving pretty smoothly
since then, huh?
-We've almost got them.
-So one of these people--
mm, mm-- is Kira.
-Well, then.
Now that everyone's here, let's
commence our regular meeting.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: But if
there's supposed to be eight,
why are there only seven?
[theme music]
LIGHT: Ryuzaki, you think I'm
capable of becoming a murderer?
Kira?
Even after I helped
you catch him?
Do I seem like that
kind of person to you?