[opening theme song]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Regardless of
how she came to the conclusion,
the fact remains-- this
woman knows the truth.
If she gives this
information to the police,
it won't take them
very long to figure out
that Kira is actually me.
I have no choice but
to eliminate her.
MAKI: Something wrong?
-Oh, eh, it's nothing.
But the more I think about
it, the more your theory
makes sense to me.
We can't waste any time.
We need to start
investigating it right away.
-What?
Really?
Do you mean that?
-Yes.
So have you told
anyone else about this?
-No you're the first
person I've told.
-[laughs] You're lucky.
But how will you get rid of her?
It's not like you
can do it here.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Well, you have
a gift for stating
the obvious, Ryuk.
-Ah, hah.
Aren't you bold?
-Let's get started.
Could you please tell me the
date and time of the busjacking
incident?
-It was December 20th, in front
of Asagao Hill at 11:02 AM,
bound for Spaceland.
-December 20th, and they were
on their way to Spaceland.
MAKI: Yes.
RYUK: [long laugh]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): This way
no one will find her body.
And even if they
do, they'll just
assume that the
death of her fiance
drove her to commit suicide.
RYUK: [laughs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Hmm?
What's so funny, Ryuk?
L: I apologize for questioning
all of you like that,
but I'm afraid I
had no other choice.
I've determined that
Kira is not among us.
[relieved sighs]
-Ryuzaki, how can you be
certain that we're all innocent?
-Well, to be honest,
from the beginning
I set a number of traps that
would reveal if any of you
was Kira.
But after speaking with you one
on one, I don't feel the need.
Excuse me.
MATSUDA (VOICEOVER):
Unbelievable.
He tells us to turn
off our cellphones.
-Understood.
I'm just about
finished here anyway.
You've got the key,
so let yourself in.
Watari's on his way.
[gasps]
-So that's everything.
I'd like to report this
incident to my father--
if it's OK with you, that is.
-Well, if it's all the same,
I think I'd like to report it
myself.
And after talking
to you, I've decided
that it would be best to
do it as soon as possible.
-Uh, that makes sense.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Just
10 seconds until 1:15.
I have to admit, I'd really
love to see how she dies.
But I can't be caught
following her around.
Go on.
Hurry to your death.
-Kira will definitely be
caught-- don't you think?
-Uh huh.
Hm.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
It should've happened already.
This doesn't make sense.
I don't understand
why she's not leaving.
I've had no problems making
people kill themselves
in the past.
All I had to do is
write the word suicide.
The criminals I tested
it on all hung themselves
exactly when I specified.
My experiments indicate that
in a situation like this,
I should be able to
control a person's actions.
So what's wrong?
RYUK: [laughs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Ryuk--
he laughed just like that
when I was writing
in the Death Note.
And that's not all.
I remember thinking
it was bizarre
how he laughed when
I asked for her name.
In fact, he's reacted
the same way every time
her name comes up.
An alias!
[gasps]
-Gentlemen, it's an
honor to meet all of you.
-This person is Watari?
-Um, what about
your usual outfit?
-If I dressed like that, I'd
be announcing to the world
that I am Watari.
That's all it takes to
give away the location
of our headquarters and Ryuzaki.
-Oh, I see.
-Ordinarily, I would never
show my face to any of you.
The fact that I'm here
is proof that you've
won Ryuzaki's trust.
-Now that you mention
it, I do feel honored.
-Well, then.
I brought those
items you requested.
It's all here.
-Could you please pass
them out to everyone?
-Yes.
Gentlemen, these are
your new police IDs.
-But-- what for?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): She used
an alias, that has to be it.
Ryuk knew all along.
He could see her real
name with his eyes.
That's why he wouldn't
stop laughing.
I should've known.
She's been overly cautious
from the beginning.
I see.
It makes a lot of sense.
She believes that
Raye died because he
showed his ID to Kira.
So of course she'd be careful
not to reveal her own identity.
Oh, this isn't good.
It's gonna be almost impossible
to ask for her real name
knowing she gave me an
alias the first time.
If I'm too persistent,
she'll get suspicious.
What am I saying?
It'll look suspicious
that I even
knew she was using an alias.
-I should probably
be getting back soon.
-Hmm?
-Someone from the task force
might be back there by now.
-Oh, yeah.
You could be right.
Let's cross our fingers
and hope someone's there.
-Yeah.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
I'm running out of options here.
I have to stop this
before it's too late.
Oh, no.
What if my father
calls back now?
I already promised her that I'd
let her talk to him if he did.
This phone rings,
it's all over for me.
What am I gonna do?
This is crazy, all I have to
do is turn my cell phone off.
Problem solved.
Now, calm down.
You know what needs to be done,
just find out her real name.
Her purse, her
pockets-- she's got
to have a driver's
license or some kind
of personal identification
on her somewhere.
She's a woman, after all.
I suppose if I had
to, I could use force.
No.
No, the last thing I want to
do is make a scene in public.
I've got to get her
somewhere isolated.
But where?
And what explanation
could I give her?
Ah, it would never
work, she's too careful.
I need a better approach.
I can do this.
I'm going to convince her
to give me her real name.
RYUK: [laughs] Hey, Light.
You know, that deal I
mentioned is still open.
It's just like putting
on contact lenses.
Completely painless.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Would I be
willing to give up half my life
just so I could learn
this woman's real name?
No, I wouldn't.
In fact, it's not even
worth considering.
Now quit wasting my time!
Just shut your mouth, shinigami.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
-Uh, do you still have business
at the police station, then?
I'd like to go there by
myself, if you don't mind.
-Yeah.
No problem.
SOICHIRO: Our names
and ranks are false.
UKIDA: Why did you
give us fake IDs?
-As you know, Kira requires
a name and a face to kill.
We will confront him with
that premise in mind.
And I think it should
be obvious why.
-Yes, but, of all people, the
police shouldn't use fake IDs.
-Enough.
What choice do we
really have, given
the capabilities of our enemy?
As long as you're
working on this case,
I think we're going to need
all the protection one can get.
It would be foolish
not to use them.
-Yeah, you got a good point.
-Uh huh.
-Remember, any time you're
in a situation where
you have to give out
your name to a stranger,
make sure to use the
name from your fake ID.
Understood?
Right, and be careful
not to take them
out while in the presence
of other police officers.
I'm sure I don't
need to tell you
that could cause
problems for us.
-I understand.
WATARI: Very well, then.
I'd like to request that
you wear these at all times.
-Uh, belts?
-Each one has a transmitter
hidden in the buckle.
This will allow Ryuzaki to
monitor your whereabouts.
And when you press the
buckle twice like this,
my cell phone will ring,
displaying your name.
And I'll call you
back immediately,
but you won't see
my number displayed.
In the morning,
all of you will go
to the police station as usual.
Then, later on in the
day, we'll use this method
to confirm the name of Ryuzaki's
hotel and his room number.
Please use this for
emergencies as well.
-No way, this is totally cool!
I feel like some kinda secret
agent going after Kira.
-Quiet, Matsuda!
This is not the time
to be fooling around.
Knock it off!
-Yes, sir.
-Thank you so much for
everything you've done, Light.
After talking to you, I
feel much more confident
about my theory.
-Not at all.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Considering
that Ryuk mentioned
that eye deal again,
there's no doubt in my mind
that she used an alias.
At this rate, once she goes
to the police with her theory
about Kira being on
that bus, and they
look at all the people Raye
Pember was investigating,
it won't take them
long to zero in on me.
-[laughs] Hey, she's leaving.
So now what?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I've
got about five minutes
before that woman gets
to police headquarters.
Think.
I need her real name.
And I don't have
much time to spare.
If this woman makes it
to the police station
and someone from the task
force has returned by then,
it'll all be over for me.
I've gotta find
out her real name,
then eliminate her quickly.
Only three minutes left until
she reaches the station.
All right.
-Oh?
Whatcha doing?
-Excuse me?
-Yes?
-There's something that I
should probably tell you.
-OK.
-The thing is,
it'll be impossible
for you to contact anyone
from the task force directly.
-Huh?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): That's right,
keep the conversation going.
I just need to find something
that she can latch onto
and I've got her.
When she's comfortable, then
I can get her real name.
I can do this.
-I can't contact anyone?
But why not?
-Didn't you find
it odd that there
was no one at task
force headquarters?
-Uh, yeah.
I did find it a bit
strange, but I didn't--
-Let me explain.
The task force
has been organized
so that its members
can't be identified
and nobody on the outside
knows who's in charge.
If The member's names
were ever made public
or the structure of the
task force was revealed,
we'd likely see another
tragedy along the lines
of the one that claimed
your fiance's life.
-I see.
-That's why you
were told earlier
that no one was at task
force headquarters.
What I'm trying to
say is, you'll never
be able to talk to someone
directly from the task force,
because the police
simply won't allow it.
-[laughs] That's pretty clever.
I'm impressed.
-If this is supposed
to be a secret,
then how do you know so much?
-Guess I spoke too soon.
She's sharp.
-Very well.
You leave me no choice.
It's because I'm actually
a member of the task force.
-Huh?
-I'm sorry, you're telling
me that you're an agent?
-Yes.
L is currently in
charge of the task force
and he's leading
our investigation.
-Yes.
To be honest, I
already suspected that.
-He was concerned that the task
force had become too small.
Many detectives had quit,
fearing for their lives,
and so, despite the fact that
I'm a high school student,
he brought me on board to help
out with the investigation.
After all, I've helped them
solve cases in the past.
-So L trusts you, then?
-I can go to task
force headquarters
whenever it suits
me, and I'm allowed
to investigate
freely as I see fit.
You see, these
days the task force
is made up of a chosen
few, an elite group
of people hand-picked
for the job by L. All
are highly skilled, well
respected, and, above all,
trustworthy.
-Oh.
-[laughs]
-Thanks for explaining,
but just to be safe,
I'd like to try and visit the
task force headquarters again.
-Huh?
-Goodbye.
-Uh, please.
Wait a second.
It's like I just told you, they
won't let you talk to anyone.
-I know, but-- I was hoping I
could speak with L directly.
-Oh, and come to think of it--
who's at the police station
right now?
-Actually, no one's
there at the moment.
-That's not good news.
We need someone
there at all times.
Work in shifts if you have to.
-I understand.
Aizawa.
I'll put you in charge
of that for today.
-Yes sir.
I'm on my way.
Won't take me long.
-Ms. Maki, please--
wait a second.
It's literally impossible to
meet L. This is pointless.
-You may be right, but
I think that there's
a chance that
he'll meet with me.
-Huh?
-Although the only
contact I've had with him
was following orders
through a computer,
he might remember who I am.
You see, I worked under
him in a case in the US
about two years ago.
-Uh, are you serious?
You worked under L?
-Yes I didn't tell you this,
but up until three months ago,
I worked as an FBI agent.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): This is it.
Finally, something I can use.
-Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
In fact, I noticed early on
that your investigative skills
were far beyond
those of an amateur.
You're very cautious
and you seem
to have a gift for getting
to the heart of the matter.
If I could, I'd like
to learn from you.
-[laughs] One lie after another.
You make it look easy.
-From the beginning,
I knew I had
to do things outside
the regular channels
because, from my perspective,
both the police and the members
of the task force were suspects.
But I'm certain that I can
trust L. Maybe it's unrealistic,
but I think that if
I go to headquarters
and I give them my name,
there's a chance that they'll
let me speak with him directly.
-I see.
But if the only person you
could trust with this info
was L, then-- why me?
-I suppose I was upset that they
wouldn't allow me to see anyone
from the task force,
and then you came along,
claiming to be the son of
the lead detective -- no,
that's not it.
I-- I'll be honest with you.
It's because you
remind me of L. There's
something about you
that's just like him.
-Will you investigate
this case with me?
-Huh?
-I want you to come work with
us as part of the task force.
We could use your help.
As I'm sure you know, not
just anyone can do it.
Please, I know this is
sudden, but the team
needs people like you.
I'm serious.
You could be doing so much
more than gathering information
on your own.
You have all the
experience as an FBI agent.
You're more talented than
most of the detectives
currently on the task
force, and L obviously
trusted you in the past.
It wouldn't be that
difficult for you to join.
All you'd need is some
valid identification,
a recommendation from a
current task force member,
and of course you'd need
to get L's permission.
-You want me to
join the task force?
-I can't help but think
that it must be fate
that I met you today.
I'd like to be the
one to recommend you.
Oh, I'm sorry about that.
I guess I got a little
bit too excited.
-It's OK.
-I mean, even if you
acted as a consultant
on this investigation,
it would be a great help.
I'm sure you have personal
obligations to attend to,
not to mention the fact that
you live in the United States.
-It's true, before
all this happened,
I thought I'd continue living
in America with my fiance.
We'd planned on getting
married in the spring.
But now he's gone, so I'm
not sure what to do anymore.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): All
right, I've come this far.
All she needs is a
little encouragement.
-But you're young and
beautiful and you've
got your life ahead of you.
Why put it all in
danger for this?
-No!
Now that Raye's gone, I've
got nothing to lose any more.
I want to catch Kira.
I don't care about
anything else.
It's all I want to do.
Please, let me investigate
this case with you.
-Huh?
[unhinged laughing]
-Yes, of course.
I just need to see some
form of identification
before we proceed.
-Oh!
Um--
-Yes?
-You see, the name
I gave you earlier,
well-- it wasn't
actually my real name.
I'm so sorry.
-Don't worry.
It's all right.
To be honest, I'm impressed
by how incredibly thorough
you've been.
You've stayed one
step ahead of me.
But I suppose that's
just further proof
of your capabilities.
-So will a Japanese driver's
license do the trick, then?
-Sure.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I made it in time.
-Uh, so, if you
don't mind my asking,
why do you keep
checking your watch?
-Oh.
Well, I guess it's
because-- because I'm Kira.
-[gasps]
-What's the matter?
-There's something I have to do.
-Hmm.
My father's cellphone
might be available now.
Do you want to see if
you can talk to him?
-No, thank you.
I have nothing to say to him.
-Then goodbye, Naomi Misora.
[ending theme song]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
With Ryuk's information
and my preparations, I can
continue to kill criminals
while masquerading as a typical
high school student studying
for his entrance exams.
Just watch me, L.