[music playing]
[music - nightmare, "the world"]
-Uh.
-Huh?
-Uh--
-I am L.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): This is him?
TOUTA MATSUDA (VOICEOVER): Hm.
He's nothing like
I thought he'd be.
-Hm.
I'm Yagami of the NPA.
-Uh, Matsuda.
-I'm Aizawa.
-Mogi.
-Ukita.
-I'm very sorry we're late.
Currently the five of us are--
-Bang.
-Uh!
-Wha?
-Uh?
-What the hell was that?
-Hm.
If I were Kira, you'd be
dead, Mr. Soichiro Yagami,
chief of the NPA.
-Wha?
-Kira needs a face and a name
in order to commit murder.
But I'm sure you've already
figured that much out,
haven't you?
Please do not give out
your names so carelessly.
Instead, let's value our lives.
-I knew that he needed
a face to kill someone,
but I don't remember
any evidence that
showed that he
needed a name, too.
-There's no way to verify
if this is related,
but criminals whose names
were never released publicly
or whose names were spelled
incorrectly in the media
have not been targeted.
We briefly went over it
at one of our meetings.
L: That's enough
small talk for now.
Come this way.
-Oh, uh, right.
L: Please turn off all
your cellphones, handhelds,
and any other
communication devices
and leave them on the
table right there.
-What, do you think we're going
to be using our cellphones
during this meeting
to leak information?
-It's all right.
Just do as he says.
TOUTA MATSUDA: I realize
he's been cautious
from the very
beginning, but I still
can't tell if he
trusts us or not.
L: No, I just find
them distracting.
I can't stand it when
people's cell phones are
ringing while I'm
trying to talk.
Let me start by saying nobody
takes notes on anything
that's said in these meetings.
That means when we
leave headquarters,
any information we need
is committed to memory.
Please, make
yourselves comfortable.
-Uh, right.
[slurps]
[gulp]
-Mm.
-Excuse me, L?
L: Mm.
And from now on, I'll have to
ask that you stop calling me
L. It's Ryuzaki now,
just to be safe.
-Uh, OK, Ryuzaki.
If we know that he needs
a name and a face to kill,
couldn't we cut down on
the number of victims
by keeping criminals'
names from the news?
-If we do that, we'll only
be putting the general public
at risk.
-The general public?
Why?
-Kira is childish
and he hates losing.
-But how do you--
-Just what do you mean?
-Well, I'm also childish
and I hate to lose.
That's how I know.
-Ryuzaki, would you mind being
a little more specific for us?
-Early on in the
investigation, I
tried to provoke Kira
with that broadcast.
Up until then we thought
that Kira would only
go after criminals, but
as we all witnessed,
he didn't hesitate
to kill my stand-in.
Also, as soon as I said we knew
he was in the Kanto region,
in defiance he made
sure his next victims
came from within
Japan, as if to say,
and what are you
going to do about it?
He's met each of my
challenges head-on
and he's never
missed an opportunity
to return the favor.
Now what do you
think would happen
if we tried to use media
restrictions to hide criminals
from someone like that?
-I guess--
-"If you choose to withhold the
names of your worst criminals,
I'll kill petty criminals
or the innocent.
I'm holding the whole world
hostage, so who's it gonna be?
I'm not the evil
one here, but all
those who oppose me
by hiding criminals?
You are truly evil."
[sigh] That's exactly
how Kira thinks.
In any case, let's
look at another way
we can use the media
to draw him out.
-But how?
-How about something like this?
"Death of FBI agents
infuriates the US.
Latest killings anger the
international policing
community.
Nations agree to send 1,500
investigators to Japan."
For Kira, this will
be way beyond what
he faced with the FBI.
He'll see everyone as
a potential threat.
Psychologically he'll
start to feel cornered,
and that will cause him to take
some kind of drastic action.
-That-- that's interesting.
-So he'll think there are
1,500 when there are really
only seven of us.
And since none of these
investigators exists,
Kira won't be able to kill them.
-It just might work.
-Well, before we
celebrate, I'll tell you
the rest of my thoughts
on the Kira case.
[all murmur]
-Kira works alone.
He had access to all our
classified information.
-What evidence do you have
that he's working alone?
-Hold on, Aizawa.
Let's listen to his entire
theory before asking questions.
-We know he needs a
name and a face to kill,
and to some extent, he can
control a victim's time
of death and their
actions before dying.
We already know that much.
Please keep that
in mind and listen
carefully to what
I have to say next.
On December 14, 12 FBI
investigators enter Japan.
Here we are on December 19.
Using prison inmates,
Kira conducts experiments,
manipulating his victims'
actions before they die.
In other words, during this
window of only five days,
Kira became aware of
the FBI's presence
and obviously felt threatened.
Because he didn't know any
of their names or faces,
he was at a disadvantage.
He needed to know how much
control he had over his victims
before he could use it
against the 12 agents.
And as we all know,
on December 27--
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I got
a hold of a file which
contained all the names and
faces of the FBI investigators
in Japan and I succeeded in
killing each one of them.
It's practically
impossible to guess
which agent gave
the file to Kira,
but I have to make sure
that no one ever finds out
that I came into contact
with Raye Pember.
-Huh?
How come you're not using
the Death Note today?
You studying for
those entrance exams?
-Those are the
least of my worries.
Plus, it's a little
late to start now.
-Oh?
What you doing?
LIGHT: December
19 to December 27.
I've been most active
during this period.
L: During this period, to
the best of our knowledge,
at least 23 individuals
died of heart attacks.
But these victims were different
from Kira's previous targets.
They were all alleged
criminals, ex-convicts,
or suspects in ongoing
investigations.
So legally speaking,
they were innocent.
-That's true.
-What this indicates
is that Kira
had to manipulate these
lesser criminals in order
to kill those FBI agents.
He killed that
many people so we'd
be unable to tell
the decoys from those
who were actually used.
In truth, he probably
only needed a few.
He waited eight days so
the FBI could investigate
other suspects, which meant
there'd be no time line linking
him to their deaths.
I suspect Kira had to be one of
the people being investigated
by the FBI between the 14th
and the 19th of December.
In fact, I have no doubt.
These are files
provided by the FBI,
and they contain
additional information
you might find useful.
For obvious reasons,
you're not permitted
to take these out
of this room, but--
TOUTA MATSUDA: Amazing!
There might only be five of
us, but with this information
we should be able to
cover a lot of ground.
-We'll split into two teams.
One team traces the FBI agents.
The other looks at the
heart attack victims.
-There weren't that many people
who had access to information
from headquarters, and
of those, the FBI only
investigated a small group
in the first five days.
-Yeah.
Yeah.
-So does anyone
have any questions?
-Uh?
-Actually, Ryuzaki, I do
have one question for you,
and it pertains to what you
said to us earlier about how
you hate to lose.
Is the fact that you've
shown us your face mean
that you've lost?
By just being here, are you
admitting defeat to Kira?
-That's right.
By showing my face to you
now and by sacrificing
the lives of 12 FBI agents,
I have lost the battle.
But I'm not going
to lose the war.
This is the first time I've
ever put my life on the line.
I want to show
Kira that we're all
willing to risk our lives if
that's what it takes-- hmf,
and that justice will
prevail no matter what.
-Hey, yeah, that's right.
-I like the sound of that.
-We can do this.
-All right, then.
Let's do this, Ryuzaki.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI (VOICEOVER):
Well, I had my doubts about
whether it was
really him at first,
but there's no mistaking it.
This man is L.
-Before we go any
further, I have
to be absolutely sure
that none of you are Kira,
so I'll need to speak
with each of you
individually before
you leave today.
-Huh.
What's the deal?
He still doesn't trust us?
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: No, I
think it's a fair request.
Try to see it from
his perspective.
Kira's been getting information
from our headquarters
from the very beginning,
so there's a good chance
that he's one of us.
-Chief's right.
Working this case has given us
a chance to see him in person.
-He's risking his
life to be here.
L (VOICEOVER): Things
are going well.
Just one clue, a single
decisive factor's all I need.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Just one oversight.
A single piece of evidence
is all it would take.
It could cost me my life.
BOTH (VOICEOVER):
Just one thing.
RYUK: You already
finished studying?
-I guess.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I'll be fine.
I haven't missed anything.
The biggest risk
I've taken so far
was that bus-jacking incident.
But they'll never be able
to connect it with Kira.
Fortunately for me,
both the police and L
don't know that
Kira can kill people
by means other than
a heart attack.
However, if anyone were
to discover that fact,
I'd be in a lot of trouble.
-What?
Does it have to be now?
-Your father's been
pulling overnighters
with no change of
clothes, so you're
going to bring these to him.
-But Mom, I totally
promised my friends
that I'd go out with them today.
-Why don't I go?
I could use a break.
-Thanks, Light.
I owe you one next time.
-So I guess this will give you
a chance to spy on the police.
-I won't go further
than the reception desk.
RYUK: Oh, you're
bringing a page.
Planning to kill someone?
-No, but lately I've been
bringing a page with me
every time I go
out, just in case.
[train rumbles on tracks]
NAOMI (VOICEOVER):
That day Raye said
he was planning
to go to Shinjuku.
That same day four people
died of heart attacks
in the Shinjuku area, and
there was the bus-jacking.
There's no way it
was a coincidence.
[slow footsteps]
NAOMI (VOICEOVER): That's it!
Kira can kill in other ways.
It doesn't have to
be a heart attack.
FEMALE SPEAKER (ON PHONE):
The mobile customer
you are trying to reach
is currently unavailable.
-That's unusual for Dad.
[beep]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): I wonder if
he's in a meeting right now.
NAOMI: Please, I need to
speak directly with someone
from the special
investigation task force.
It's urgent.
-I'm sorry, ma'am,
but I can't help you.
As I've told you
already, there is no one
at task force
headquarters right now.
-[sighs]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): There's
no one at headquarters?
Dad's cell is turned off.
What's going on?
-Can't you contact them somehow?
I have information relating
to the Kira investigation.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): The
Kira investigation?
-Look, I'll call headquarters
one more time for you.
One moment.
-Hi, I'm Detective Soichiro
Yagami's son, Light Yagami.
I brought my father
a change of clothes,
but it doesn't
look like he's in.
Can I leave them here?
-Sure.
Hey, I haven't seen
you in a while, Light.
-Oh, I'm sorry, uh--
-What, you don't remember?
You helped solve the insurance
fraud murder investigation
sometime last year.
But hey, no one remembers
the receptionist, do they?
-Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm terrible with faces.
I just need to sign my
name on this form, right?
-So, Light, does
this mean you're
going to be helping us with
the Kira investigation, too?
-Sure.
If all goes well, maybe I'll
find Kira before L does.
NAOMI (VOICEOVER):
Find him before L does?
-As I thought, there's
no one at headquarters.
You're going to have to
trust me on this, ma'am.
I'll be sure to give them your
message as soon as I see them.
I promise.
-That's not good enough.
I have to tell them in person.
LIGHT: Excuse me.
My father is actually in charge
of the Kira investigation.
If you'd like, I could pass
your message on to him.
His cell phone is
off at the moment,
but I should be able
to contact him soon.
A number of FBI agents were just
killed, and a lot of detectives
have quit the case because
they're afraid of Kira.
So he's pretty busy right now.
-Uh, Light, it's probably
better if you don't discuss this
with--
-True, but it's practically
common knowledge at this point.
Besides, I feel like
I can trust her.
You can almost see
it in her eyes.
She's a wise and careful person.
You heard about what happened
and you must have figured out
that the police had
a leak of some kind,
and that's why you wanted
to tell them in person.
You've thought this through.
Well, am I right?
I'm sure my father
will be calling me back
once he checks his messages.
When he does, I'll give you the
phone and let you talk to him.
-You're sure that's all right?
-Oh, yeah.
You understand why I can't just
give you my father's cell phone
number.
But I have no
problem letting you
use my phone to talk to him.
You'll have to trust my father
and I, which I hope won't
be too difficult
for you. [laughs]
RYUK (VOICEOVER):
Why is he so happy?
-Thank you so much.
--[cackles] She walked right
into that one, didn't she?
LIGHT: I've got to
say, you must be
pretty brave to be getting
involved in the Kira case
like this.
-Hmph, not really.
-So according to you, is
Kira some-- [clears throat].
Um, we've been
talking and I just
realized I don't
even know your name.
My name is Light Yagami.
Light's written with
the character for moon,
and Yagami with the
characters for night and god.
Kind of weird, huh?
-My name's Shoko Maki.
It's written with the
characters for shining,
"ko" as in "child," "space,"
and "ki" as in "tree."
-Miss Maki, right?
-[cackles]
LIGHT: Miss Maki, I've been
thinking about Kira's powers,
and I believe they enable
him to somehow control
his victims before they die.
-So do I!
It's odd that you say
that, because that's
exactly what I've been thinking.
Kira's able to control their
actions before he kills them,
but there's more to it.
If my analysis so
far is correct,
Kira can kill in
a number of ways,
not just with a heart attack.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): She knows?
Who is this woman?
-I don't think anyone
else knows this yet,
but if the police are
willing to consider it
I bet it would help
them catch Kira.
-You know, that possibility
never even crossed my mind.
So what you're saying
is any time Kira wants
one of his murders
to go undetected,
he wouldn't use a heart attack.
-Right.
I'm almost positive that someone
I know may have met Kira.
-Met Kira?
[laughs] I'm sorry, but if a
person came in saying they'd
met Kira, the police
would be more than a
little skeptical,
to say the least.
-I know.
That's why I need to explain
it in person to someone
from task force headquarters.
Otherwise I'm afraid
they'll just write me off.
-But wouldn't it be
better if your friend
spoke to them instead?
-It probably would, but
he's no longer alive.
He was one of the
12 FBI agents who
came to Japan to
investigate Kira.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): An
FBI agent who met Kira?
Could it be?
NAOMI: You see, he
was also my fiance.
While he was working he got
caught up in a bus-jacking,
and I have reason to believe
that he met Kira on that bus.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Raye Penber.
-Is something wrong?
-Nothing.
I'm sorry to hear
that he passed away.
So what makes you think
he met Kira on that bus?
-Because eight days after
that bus was hijacked,
he died along with the
other FBI investigators.
The same man had attempted to
rob a bank two days before he
hijacked that bus, then he dies
in an accident, just like that?
I mean, really,
what are the odds?
I've come to believe that
Kira set up that bus-jacking.
It was planned to bring him
into contact with my fiance
in order to obtain
information regarding
the identities of
the other FBI agents
so he could get rid of them all.
Anyway, what stands out to
me is that the hijacker died
in an accident.
In other words, it
suggests that heart attacks
aren't the only way
Kira can kill people.
-OK, so the bus-jacker
didn't die of a heart attack.
And based on that,
you're saying Kira
has other ways of
killing people?
-Yes.
-Don't take this
the wrong way, but I
think that's a bit
of a leap of faith.
-There's no other
way of looking at it.
If Kira was controlling
the hijacker,
chances are he killed him too.
-I still don't see it.
-I've been wondering
about that bus-jacking
ever since my fiance
first told me about it.
After he calmed down, I
asked him for details.
He didn't mention any names
or anything like that,
but he told me one thing.
LIGHT: What did he say?
-That he'd been put
in a situation where
he had to show his
FBI ID to someone.
-Hm.
-The operation was
undertaken secretly
without the NPA's knowledge.
He wasn't allowed
to show his ID.
I think whoever
saw his ID that day
is responsible for the
deaths of all the agents.
RYUK (VOICEOVER): Unbelievable.
She figured it out.
This must be the oversight
Light was worried about.
-I understand.
You're the only one
who knows any of this
and you want nothing more
than to avenge your fiance
by bringing Kira
to justice, right?
And now you're
convinced that Kira
can kill without
using a heart attack.
-Yes.
LIGHT: There's no
doubt in my mind
your deductive
skills are excellent,
but you can't deny that you
have a personal interest
in the case.
Still, , your theory is worth
looking into, that's for sure.
Your testimony could
be central to the case.
-It could.
-If what you're
telling me is true,
then it'll only be
a matter of time
before the police
catch up with Kira.
The person your fiance
showed his ID to on the bus
that day-- it had to be Kira.
-That's right.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
That was close.
This woman, if she'd
spoken to the police
before I met her--
but it seems there's
a god on my side after all,
and not just a god of death.
[slow footsteps]
[music - nightmare, "alumina"]
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I have to admit
I'd really love to
see how she dies,
but I can't be caught
following her around.
Go on.
Hurry to your death.