[theme music]
-Wow, it's been a long time.
Thank you for always taking
such good care of my father.
-Gee, Sayu.
You're all grown up.
-This is Yagami.
MELLO (ON PHONE): Look.
About trading the director
in exchange for the notebook.
It's been cancelled.
The new deal is this.
The notebook for Sayu Yagami.
Come to LA, by
yourself, in two days,
and bring the notebook with you.
-I'm pleased to meet you
at last, L number two.
I am at the center of the SPK.
You can address me as N.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): N?
Who is this guys?
Is he joking?
But this strange feeling.
What is it?
N. Why do I feel like
I'm talking to L?
NEAR (MODIFIED VOICE): I told
you that we wouldn't rely on L,
but that's a bit of
an understatement.
The FBI and the
CIA have explicitly
asked that I head up
their investigation.
Not you.
Having said that,
we are outraged
by the recent murder of
the direct of the NPA
and feel something must be done.
After revealing
the information, I
believe there's a possibility
that solving this case
could lead to the
arrest of Kira.
As such, I'm willing to
lend you my full support.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Lead
to the arrest of Kira?
Who is he anyway?
This confidence
NEAR (MODIFIED VOICE):
Is there a problem, L?
-N-- No.
It's just that, following
the death of Takimura,
Deputy Director Yagami's
daughter was kidnapped,
and we believe the same
person is behind it.
He's arranged for a
trade in Los Angeles.
NEAR (MODIFIED VOICE): A trade?
The girl in exchange for
the notebook, I assume.
-Yes.
-Understood.
I'll have a team
on standby in LA,
but for now, they'll be working
on a need to know basis.
Also, I can monitor
the city via satellite.
Or-- (MODIFIED VOICE)
On second thought,
I'll let you have full
authority on this, L.
-That's good.
It means we're taking the lead.
-But what's all this
about the Americans
not trusting L anymore?
I don't like the sound of that.
-Near, is it really
safe to leave this case
in the hands of a fake L?
He hasn't had any success
in catching Kira so far.
-I'm aware of that.
That's why it's a good idea.
It means there'll
be an opportunity
to take advantage of him.
Of course, saving people's
lives is important.
But, as the SPK, our
primary goal is very clear.
We'll work to get the
notebook and capture Kira
once and for all.
CHIEF YAGAMI: Light.
-Hm?
-At this point, I don't
care if it costs me my life.
Please, just save Sayu.
Promise me.
-Stop talking like that, dad.
You might have made your
peace with the idea of dying,
but have you ever
thought about how painful
it would be for everyone
else you leave behind?
I'd never be able to
forgive you if you ended up
dying in front of Sayu.
Look.
It's true that you might
lose contact with us.
But if that happens and you have
to make a split second decision
by yourself, then I want
you to do whatever's
necessary to make sure both you
and Sayu get out of this alive.
Promise me, dad.
-All right.
MISA: What?
No way!
You really want me to go
to Los Angeles with you?
-Yeah.
There's a chance I might need
to use your eyes this time,
so I want to have you close by.
-Oh, Light!
You're the best!
Oh, my gosh.
I better start
packing right away.
Let's see.
Which one should I bring?
I can't decide.
Light!
Which do you like?
Huh?
Hm.
-If things go badly, I
may have to kill Sayu.
Dad.
I'll fly to LA ahead
of you and make
preparations for the hand over.
Ide and the others should
arrive shortly after.
But to be safe, we should
arrive on separate flights.
Aizawa, I want you to tail
my father closely and get
on the same plane as him, just
in case something goes wrong.
AIZAWA: Got it.
I'm gonna get a haircut so
they won't recognize me.
LIGHT: OK, everyone.
I'm counting on you.
-Mr. Yagami.
-Who are you?
One of the kidnappers?
-You're going to
board flight SE333.
I have your tickets with me.
It leaves from Gate 18.
-Right.
I understand.
-Someone has intercepted
him at [inaudible].
Should I arrest him?
LIGHT: Calm down, Aizawa.
Don't make any sudden.
I can understand your
concern, but arresting him now
will accomplish nothing.
Keep your distance, and
don't lose sight of them.
-Damn it, They're boarding
a difference flight
than originally planned.
I'll tell them at the gate I'm
a police officer, and they'll--
LIGHT: Get a hold of yourself!
You'd just blow your cover
the operation would be ruined.
Can you find out where
the flight is headed?
-Let's see.
Huh?
This one's going to LA too.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Could
they have somehow arranged
for another plane.
Oh, this is bad.
MAN: Flight SE33, Flight
SE333, do you copy?
Do you copy?
You have strayed from
your flight path.
PILOT: This is Flight SE333.
I read you loud and clear.
I assure you, everything's OK.
This is a detour.
-What the-- What is this?
You need to tell me,
what's going on up there?
-This is not a hijacking.
We're simply making a
detour, and a quick stop
to drop off a passenger.
You can track us by radar.
However, if you attempt to call
the authorities to interfere
with our course, I will not
hesitate to crash the plane
and take all the
passengers with me.
-This is bad, Light.
I mean L. The deputy
director's flight has just
changed direction.
A passenger's gonna be
dropped off somewhere.
It can only be him.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
What the hell is going on?
I already checked today's flight
crews and passenger lists ahead
of time.
No one on board was suspicious.
The pilot's a veteran
of over 15 years.
The co-pilot checks
out clean, too.
Then the kidnappers
are powerful enough
to influence these people.
Looks like I have no choice.
Director, this is L. Get me N.
-Right.
LIGHT (ON PHONE): N.
I'm sure you're aware
of our current situation.
I need you to do me a favor.
Can you notify the airline's
police and military
on your end not to
take any action yet?
-What's he thinking?
I never realized he
was this unreliable.
-All right, L. Agreed.
We'll locate the landing
site and keep surveillance
over the area using our
satellite video feed.
If there's anything
else we can do,
don't hesitate to let us know.
-I have a message for you.
Put this in your ear.
MELLO (ON EARPIECE): Yagami.
Right now, you're the only
one who can hear my voice.
Listen very carefully.
I'm the one who
kidnapped your daughter.
But don't get the wrong idea.
I have no interest in
your daughter's life one
way or the other, or
yours, for that matter.
There's only one thing I want,
and you know what that is.
The notebook.
Now, all you have to do
is follow my instructions.
If you do that,
no one has to die.
As for the trade, I've prepared
things so that both of us
can walk away satisfied.
Play along, and
there'll be no problems.
CHIEF YAGAMI
(VOICEOVER): I'm going
to give the notebook to
some criminal in exchange
for my daughter's life.
When the time comes, what's
the right thing to do?
As a police officer, as a
human being, and as a parent?
[ringing]
-L, we've been able to
use our satellite cameras
to pinpoint where
the plane has landed.
I'll send you a
direct video feed
of what we're
currently seeing here.
-Dad.
-Heh, heh, heh.
So what's going to happen?
How will he make the exchange
in a place like that?
MELLO: You see the
entrance, don't you, Yagami?
Go inside.
-They're underground?
-Well, well.
Isn't that interesting?
-Dammit.
An underground facility?
The kidnapper must
have predicted
that we'd be watching
him by satellite.
That means there's no way
to keep an eye on Dad.
[gunshots]
-The glass is bulletproof.
Understand?
This place used to belong
to a crime syndicate.
They used to make
trades just like this.
We've made a few
modifications, as well.
Slide the notebook through here.
Once that's done,
I'll release the lock.
We'll both step back
and spin the glass door.
The notebook will end up on my
side, and the girl on yours.
However, if you don't
agree to this trade,
I'll shoot your daughter
through this opening.
NEAR (MODIFIED VOICE):
L, do you have a plan?
You can't seriously think
that handing the notebook over
to someone you don't know
is it good idea, can you?
-All right, Y462.
Proceed.
-First, open the notebook
and insert it halfway
into the slot in the
glass door on your left.
-(VOICEOVER) Dammit,
dammit, dammit.
It's setback after setback.
And I've only just
arrived in the US,
so I'm not in any position
to start giving orders
to the American police.
At this rate, the
notebook's gonna be--
-Light, is everything OK?
Is something wrong?
You look kind of--
-Misa, just shut up and do
what I told you, all right?
Look, I need you to keep
killing Japanese criminals,
so just do that.
This guy's obviously
investigating Kira,
and he won't give up.
If the killings are
delayed, we're in trouble.
Don't you understand?
-Uh-- OK.
But who is this guy?
-Just get on with
it, all right!?
-Taking out your
anger on her, huh?
-Hm?
-(VOICEOVER) I
can still make it.
But at this rate, is my
only option to kill Sayu?
-Now, then, I'll
test the notebook.
-Test it?
You're going to kill someone?
No, I can't allow that.
-We can't make the
trade without making
sure it's the real thing.
Do you really want to
see your daughter die?
-(VOICEOVER) I can't do it.
No one but the police
knows about this case.
If Sayu dies, I can't
blame her death on Kira.
-What's wrong?
You OK, Miller?
-Look.
That's what you get
when you steal from me
and sell goods behind my back.
He was a worthlss idiot.
This is the first
time he's been useful.
-Y462, the target is dead.
-It seems the notebook
is genuine after all.
Now let it go.
We'll make the exchange
for your daughter.
-Dad.
Sayu.
-Hey, they actually made it.
-The suspect is headed
for a helicopter.
Based on our intel, that's his
only method of transportation.
-So this means we can
be absolutely certain
that the notebook
has been exchanged.
-Be careful.
We still don't know
what they're planning
to do beyond this point.
N, I need you to maintain
surveillance of that helicopter
until it lands.
Don't lose sight of
it, no matter what.
-You seem to think that's
quite an easy task.
Nevertheless, we'll
do what we can.
(MODIFIED VOICE) I'm sorry.
I'm afraid we've been tricked.
-Huh?
A missile?
-Whoa.
-We won't be able to
track that with radar.
-Is the notebook on that thing?
-The missile's been launched.
-The missile or the helicopter?
Which one?
-Boss, I'm sure
you were watching.
I did everyting you asked
me to, just let we planned.
-Yeah, I saw that.
Good job.
-Then this is going to wipe
out all those past screw
ups of mine, right?
-Oh, yeah.
Wiped out for sure.
Do it.
-Near, the helicopter.
-I thought so.
-In that case, it means
the notebook is definitely
on the missile.
-Damn!
We can't track it.
We've lost the signal.
It could be anywhere now.
-It won't be difficult
to retrieve the missile
once it lands in
a deserted area.
He would have already laid out
the flight plan accordingly.
Should be getting his hands on
the notebook any moment now.
And when he does, I have a good
idea of what he'll do next.
[groan]
[gunshot]
[beeping]
NEAR: (MODIFIED VOICE) L.
-Yes?
NEAR: (MODIFIED
VOICE) He got us.
-Got you?
NEAR: (MODIFIED VOICE) Yes.
The majority of
the SPK's members
have just been killed
by the notebook.
L, you were the one who
handed over the notebook
without a fight.
You and your people
were totally helpless.
-N-- are you saying if
you were in command,
you wouldn't have
handed it over?
-No.
Considering their
preparations, it
would have been
impossible to avoid this.
There's really no
point in us quarreling.
I propose we work
together and share
the information we know so far.
For starters, I
should admit that I
have a very good idea of who the
culprit behind this might be.
I suspect the
person who arranged
the kidnapping and
the trade is someone
who goes by the name Mello.
-Mello?
Who's he?
-I don't have his photograph,
and I don't know his real name.
All I know about him is
that four years ago, he
was living at an orphanage
located in Winchester, England,
known as Wammy's House.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Wammy's House?
That's the place
Watari established.
-I believe Mello is
playing a game with me.
He wants to see which of us will
be the first to take down Kira.
The final challenge.
-Uh, "Armo Justin?"
-It's Armonia Justin.
-M'kay.
Um, I've got a little problem.
I went to the king to report
that I lost my notebook,
but after I described
it to him, the old man
said that Ryuk said it was
his, and that he had dropped it
and took it.
So, what do you think I
should do to get it back?
-Guess you have no choice but to
find Ryuk and ask him yourself.
-Yeah, that's what I thought.
So, I guess I have to
go to the human world.
-Yep.
That's right.
Have fun.
-Well, that sucks.
[theme music]
LIGHT: Calm down and listen.
On November 10, 11:59 PM, all
the mafia members will die.
That moment will be
your only opportunity
to get the notebook back.