[music playing]
-That was footage from
surveillance cameras
at the station.
The death of one of the FBI
agents is captured on here.
-Let's see the
following scenes again--
Raye Penber passing the
ticket gate on his way in,
then him boarding the
train, and finally the part
where he dies on the platform.
OK.
Let's see.
-I think it's next to that.
-Oh, here it is.
-Um, so based on the
records I have here,
Ray Penber comes through
the west entrance
of Shinjuku Station at 3:11 PM.
Then at 3:13, he boards a
train on the Yamanote line.
But even if he was following
someone at that time,
I think it's going to
be very difficult for us
to draw any real conclusions
from this blurry video.
Then at exactly 4:42 PM-- oh,
thank you very much, Watari.
Um, and at 4:42 PM, he exits
a train at Tokyo station
and dies on the platform.
-It's quite strange,
don't you think?
-I'm sorry, what do
you find strange?
-Yeah, what is it?
Did you notice something?
-Mmm.
We know that Raye
Penber got on the train,
and then an hour
and a half later he
got off and died
on the platform.
But the Yamanote line
only takes an hour
to complete its circuit.
And more importantly,
there's the envelope.
-Uh, what do you mean?
L: He's holding what looks
like an envelope when
he passes through
the ticket gate.
-You're right!
It's there, under his arm.
But in the footage right
before his death, it's gone.
I can't believe you
actually caught that.
-Well, I don't see an
envelope on this list
of his personal effects.
L: Which means it was
left on the train.
And if you watch closely
at the very end here,
it seems like he's straining
to look inside the train
before the doors close.
You can see right here.
-If that's the case, do you
think it could mean something?
-Wouldn't it be interesting
if Kira was on that train.
-That's impossible.
-I admit, I find it hard
to believe, as well.
There's no reason
for Kira to come
to the scene of
his own crime when
he can kill from a distance.
Well, maybe he was counting
on us to make that assumption
and figured he could get
away with such a bold move.
Mmm.
-Mmm.
RYUK: What's going
on with you, Light?
You haven't stopped writing
criminals' names in the death
note for four days straight.
So what are you trying to prove?
I don't see the point in writing
these names weeks in advance.
I've never seen the death
note used like this.
-Consider it insurance.
Suppose the son of the detective
superintendent of the NPA
was hospitalized.
If criminals stopped
dying at the same time,
it wouldn't be difficult
to connect the two.
-So that's what this is.
-Are you sure that
I can use any date
as long as it's before the end
of a person's predetermined
lifespan?
-Well, I can't guarantee
it because we Shinigami
don't normally work that way.
But I suppose any time before
the end of their lifespan
should work.
-I really can't
count on you, can I?
-You got that right.
WATARI: Yes?
Yes.
Would you please
hold for a moment?
Ryuzaki, it's Ukita at the NPA.
He says he's on the
phone with someone
from the tip line who
has information for us.
-Right, then give Ukita
the number for line five
and ask him to
have the informant
call that line instead.
It'll be safer that way.
-Mr. Matsuda, it's OK for you
to turn on your cell phone now.
Actually, please turn
it on right away.
-Uh, sure.
-Yes, this is Suzuki, head of
Kira's investigation public
information division.
Raye Penber's fiancee?
Naomi Misora.
I've heard that name before.
So it's her.
She's from the Los
Angeles BB Murder Case.
That's right.
She was working under me.
I guess she must have come
to Japan with her fiance.
Well, apparently she's
been missing since the day
after her fiance died.
-I'm sure that anyone
in her situation
would be pretty depressed.
Was it--
-Suicide.
-No.
The Naomi Misora
I knew was strong.
Not to mention, she was
also an excellent FBI agent.
If anything, it's more likely
she'd be trying to catch Kira.
It appears she came
to Japan with Penber.
It's possible that she
may have found a lead.
If that's the case, did Kira
manage to get her first?
Everyone, at this point I'd
like to focus our investigation
on only those people who
Raye Penber was tailing.
In particular, he was assigned
to two police officers
and those closest to them.
-Very well, who are
these two individuals
he was investigating?
-Deputy Director Kitamura, along
with Detective Superintendent
Yagami and their families.
At this stage, I'd like to
place wiretaps and surveillance
cameras in both households.
-I have to make sure there's no
evidence left on this computer,
just in case someone
goes through it.
Now I just have to
hide these clippings
from the death note in here.
RYUK: It seems like you're
pretty skilled with your hands.
I bet you're pretty popular
with the girls, aren't you?
LIGHT: Skill has
nothing to do with it.
It's your looks that count.
I'm guessing you're not
that popular, are you?
Huh?
-Surveillance cameras?
Ryuzaki.
I don't see how you
could even consider this.
If this got out, we'd
have a civil rights
scandal on our hands.
We'd all lose our jobs.
-You told me you'd
be willing to risk
your lives for
this investigation,
but you wouldn't risk your jobs?
-Ryuzaki, what are
the odds that Kira's
in one of those households?
-Maybe 10%.
No, it's closer to 5%.
-Seriously?
I'm sorry, but it's
not worth the risk.
SOICHIRO YAGAMI: No.
Of all the people we've
investigated so far,
not one of them seemed even
the least bit suspicious.
Even if there's
only a 1% chance,
we simply can't
afford to ignore it.
SHUICHI AIZAWA: Chief?
-I don't have to
tell you how offended
I am to learn my family
is under suspicion.
Having said that,
just go ahead with it.
And make sure you
install them everywhere.
I don't want any blind
spots in the house,
and that includes the bathroom.
-Thank you very much.
That was my intention.
-Come on, Chief.
You don't have to agree to this.
-Yes, he's right!
Think about your family.
You have a wife and
daughter at home, don't you?
-Yes, I'm well
aware of that fact.
But there is no point
in doing any of this
if we can't be thorough.
Now I suggest you keep quiet!
-I'm sorry.
-No, it's OK.
Excuse me.
-As a courtesy to the
chief and his family,
only he and I will conduct
surveillance of their home.
Watari, how long will
it take to prepare
the wiretaps and
cameras we need?
-Well, starting tomorrow I
can set them up at any time
provided we know when
both houses will be empty.
-See you later, Light.
-Yeah, see you tomorrow.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): What?
No one's home yet.
I'm home.
Huh?
Hmm.
RYUK: How's it going?
I don't think anyone else
is in the house right no.
Do you want to play
some video games?
Come on, it's been a while.
You listening?
Hey, Light.
-I don't believe it.
I never knew he went
to such great lengths.
What could he be
hiding in there that he
doesn't want anyone else to see?
-For a 17-year-old
kid, I wouldn't
say this kind of behavior
is particularly abnormal.
When I was his age, I
did strange things, too.
Have you ever talked to your
son about the investigation?
-Of course not.
I've never once revealed
classified information
to my family.
Besides, I don't get to see
them too often these days.
And usually as soon as I get
home, all I can do is sleep.
-I understand.
-Where exactly are we going?
Light, don't ignore me when I'm
talking to you or I'll get mad.
Huh?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
It doesn't look
like these clothes
have been bugged.
RYUK: Hello?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I think we're safe.
-Yoohoo.
-Listen to me.
There's a very
strong possibility
that there are
wiretaps and maybe
surveillance cameras
hidden throughout my house.
-Really?
But that piece of paper was
still in your door, wasn't it?
-That's true, but I left the
paper in the door in a way
that it would be obvious to
anyone entering the room.
The real test is the handle.
-It is?
-When that door is
closed, the door
handle automatically returns
to a horizontal position,
and it won't go any
higher than that.
But whenever I close the
door, I adjust it slightly.
Instead of letting
it sit horizontally,
I lower it by about
five millimeters.
When I get home and I
try to open the door,
if the handle is
all the way up, I
can be fairly certain that
someone was in my room.
But that method
alone doesn't tell me
if my door was actually opened.
So I put a mechanical pencil
lead in place, as well.
-So what you do with it?
-It goes on the hinge.
After I close the door, I take
the pencil lead and rest it
on the hinge in
such a way that it
will break if the door happens
to be opened by anyone.
Normally, I take it out
myself when I get back home.
When I got home
from school today,
I noticed that the
pencil lead was broken.
-Now that you mention
it, I do remember that.
-First the door
handle, then the lead.
I know someone was
in there today.
-Maybe it was your mother.
-My family wouldn't have
noticed the piece of paper.
What's suspicious is that
someone took the time
to put it back in the door.
BOOKSTORE MERCHANT: Hi
there, can I help you?
-What's this all about?
Are you buying a book about
wiretaps and surveillance
so you can figure this mess out?
-By the way, Ryuk,
what about your apples?
-Apples?
Huh?
That's right,
surveillance cameras!
Once the apple's in my
mouth, no one can see it.
But while I'm holding it,
it looks like it's floating.
-I thought so.
You told me that
Shinigami can't die.
So I guess it won't kill you to
stop eating apples for a while.
-Uh, don't you think
that's a bit much?
Come on.
I never told you this,
but apples are to me
what cigarettes and
alcohol are to humans.
Do you see what I'm saying?
I even get withdrawal symptoms.
LIGHT: Oh yeah?
What kind of symptoms?
-My body gets all twisted.
I do handstands.
It's not pretty!
-I don't need to see that.
-I know.
-OK, here's the thing.
Unfortunately, I
already gave L the hint
that Shinigami love apples.
So I just can't afford
to take the risk.
-When did you--
-If it's so important
for you to eat apples,
you'll have to find out where
all the cameras are hidden.
If you're lucky, you
might find a blind spot
where you can eat them
without being seen.
All right, let's go.
-Yeah, a camera search!
Sounds so interesting.
[music playing]
-Oh.
Oh, uh, I have to
find the cameras.
-I can't believe my son is
looking at those magazines.
-It's normal for a 17-year-old.
But it seems contrived.
It's too obvious.
The only reason he didn't
want anyone in his room
is because he had
these magazines?
That's what he
wants us to think.
-Hey, that's my son
you're talking about.
Are you honestly telling
me that you suspect him?
-I do suspect him.
That's why I placed wiretaps
and surveillance cameras
in your house and the
deputy director's house.
-Huh?
I found a camera in
the air conditioner.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Hmm.
So they really put
cameras in here.
They must have bugged
the place, as well.
Even if this is the
Kira case, I didn't
think the Japanese police
would ever go this far.
This must be L's
idea, which means
they've narrowed down
their list of suspects.
By now they must
have figured out
that it was someone who Raye
Penber was investigating
or they wouldn't have
gone to all this trouble.
-Man, these covers
mislead you all the time.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): No.
Given the situation,
it's safer if I just
assume I'm their prime
suspect and the only one being
launched.
It'll be OK.
Luckily, I prepared for
this kind of situation.
-Oh, Light.
-Hey, Light.
Come on, dinner's ready.
-I love you always.
-Hideki Ryuga!
I swear he's perfect!
How come no one in my
class is like that?
-Sayu, just eat your dinner.
SAYU: I'll eat later.
-Hello, Mr. Aizawa?
Are the Kitamuras
watching television now?
-Yes.
He's not home,
but the other four
are watching while
they eat dinner.
It's channel four.
-Watari, please contact
the broadcasters
and tell them to
play our message.
WATARI: Very well.
Understood.
SAYU: Huh?
What's this?
ICPO?
They're saying that in
response to the Kira murders,
Interpol has decided to dispatch
a force of 1,500 investigators
to Japan.
The investigators were drawn
from the law enforcement
agencies of its member nations.
1,500 investigators?
Woah.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Chances are they've
got cameras in the
living room, as well.
Regardless of whether
this news is real or not,
it's obvious they're just trying
to evoke a reaction from me.
This is the exact same
trick he used last time.
LIGHT: The ICPO sure is stupid.
-Huh?
-I mean, there's no point
in making this announcement.
If they're going to send
all these people here
to investigate, shouldn't
they keep it a secret?
Even the FBI agents who
were secretly investigating
were killed by Kira.
Why would this be any different?
If you ask me, this is nothing
more than a desperate attempt
to shock Kira in the hopes that
he'll reveal himself somehow.
Quite frankly, I
wouldn't be surprised
if Kira sees right through this.
-Hmm.
Your son's clever, isn't he?
-Huh.
Well, yes.
LIGHT: Thanks for dinner, Mom.
SACHIKO YAGAMI: Huh?
You're eating a bag of chips?
You just had dinner.
Your good looks are
going to go down
the drain if you keep that up.
LIGHT: It's a late-night
snack for studying.
-I think that's it, Light.
I found every camera
they put in the house.
I guess Shinigami get
tired when they work hard.
Now let me explain
where they all are.
It's a little bit
complicated, so listen up.
There's nothing I hate more
than explaining something twice.
-All right.
It's time for me
to hit the books.
RYUK: There sure are a lot
of cameras in this room.
I counted 64 in total.
I guess whoever put
them here expected
you to at least
find some of them.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
It has to be L.
He had no qualms about putting
a death row inmate in his place
when he declared war on me.
It's pretty clear he
doesn't know any limits.
-Ah, what I want
to know is how am I
going to be able to eat apples?
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Obviously,
that's impossible now,
isn't it?
-Oh, yeah.
I guess you can't talk in here.
But we'd better discuss
this outside tomorrow.
-OK.
I think I'm getting
the hang of this now.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER): Judging
by the number of cameras
he's planted, he's
planning to make a decision
within a short period of time.
Any normal person would slip
under these circumstances.
But it won't be
that easy with me,
L. This is the closest you get!
I've set things up so that
criminals will continue
to die over the
next three weeks.
L is aware by now
that Kira can control
the times of death
of his victims.
Therefore, to avoid
suspicion he'll
need to see the criminals
whose names are being broadcast
continue to die while I have
no access to that information.
-Oh!
The symptoms are starting!
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
I'm gonna show you, L.
[music playing]
With Ryuk's information
and my preparations,
I can continue to kill criminals
whose names are broadcast
on the news while masquerading
as a typical high school
student studying for
his entrance exams.
Just watch me, L. I'll solve
equations with my right hand
and write names with my left.
I'll take a potato
chip and eat it!
[music playing]
-After dinner, your
son just goes back
to studying without turning
on the TV or his computer?
-It's because the entrance
exams are five days away.
LIGHT (VOICEOVER):
Now, a criminal
who I should have
no knowledge of will
die of a heart
attack in 40 seconds.
And the witness to my
alibi is L himself.
-All right.
Just a little bit longer.
-Ryuzaki.
-Yes?
What is it, Watari?
-A few minutes ago, a bank
clerk being questioned
on suspicion of embezzlement
and a purse-snatcher being
held in a detention center
were broadcast on the news.
They both just died of sudden,
inexplicable heart attacks.
-It's him again.
-While all that was
happening at your home,
your wife and daughter
were watching television.
When that was over,
they turned the TV off
and didn't want
anything afterwards.
From just about 7:30
until now, 11 o'clock,
your son's done
nothing but study.
Kira needs a name and a face.
Without those, he can't kill.
So I suppose anyone who
didn't watch the news
can't be Kira, right?
-You said it yourself.
That means my family
has been cleared.
It doesn't make sense that Kira
would kill two petty criminals
right after their
identities were broadcast.
I know it's only the first
day after the cameras were
installed, but the
Yagami household
seems almost too innocent to me.
Hmm.
SACHIKO YAGAMI:
Light, are you up yet?
-Yeah, I'm awake.
-Today's garbage day,
so if you've got any,
bring it down with you, OK?
-What a pain.
SACHIKO YAGAMI: What
are you talking about?
You usually say, there's
no need to remind me, Mom.
-Yeah, yeah.
Another beautiful day.
-Well, I can't say for sure
whether you are extremely
generous or just a spoiled brat,
but didn't that mini LCD TV
cost you $400?
-Good morning.
[music playing]
LIGHT: Perfect.
There's no reason
for me to be worried.
After all, this is proof that
they don't have anything on me yet.
So this whole thing is nothing
more than a contest between L
and I, a battle of wits.