We're out of money.
I told you the 30 yen plan
was a bad idea.
[SEIYA] (grrr)
Look, the point is,
I'm really sorry,
but we're not gonna be able to
pay anybody for this past month.
[chair rattling]
[BOTH] You're not
giving us a paycheck?!
[TIRAMY]
What's with that, mii?!
[MACARON] (hyperventilating)
Forget it! We can't give you
money we don't have!
But I have to go to the bars and
pick up all the loose women!
No, you don't.
And I have to play pachinko!
Again, no, you don't!
Listen up! I need you to help me
brainstorm some ideas
to help bring in
some quick revenue.
Betting on horses!
[SEIYA] No gambling!
Ooh! Adults‐only attractions!
[SEIYA] That's probably illegal.
Moffle Punching Bag!
[SEIYA] You're just gonna
punch right back.
I have the solution here.
[SEIYA] Uh, I'm not
sure what that is...
Come on, think!
There's gotta be another way!
[ALL] Hmm...
Ron! Here's an idea!
Let's pay a visit to
Dornell's Cave!
Dornell's Cave?
You know about the
secondary park, don't you?
Yeah, I did read a
little bit about it.
So, what's the big deal?
Dornell's Cave is
inside that park! [huh?]
Moff! A while back, there was
a flower fairy working here
by the name of Dornell.
But one dark night,
he got drunk,
and set off on a test of courage
with some of his buddies.
I don't have time for
the whole novel.
[tch!]
Anyway, they found some
treasure in that cave.
Hey, there...
Could we get two crepes please?
Uh, hello?
Huh? Didn't think it
would be this grand.
[ISUZU] The southern region was
supposed to be a second park
with a focus on sports.
This stadium was the first
element they built.
[MOFFLE] But after the bubble
burst, the plan fell apart
and they just kinda
left the building here.
[ISUZU]
It was quite disappointing.
Ever since that happened,
the entire southern area's
been completely untouched.
[hmm...]
And rumor has it Dornell never
came out of the cave again
after that night?
[MOFFLE] That's right. [ooff]
[SEIYA] Wait, you never told us
what happened to the friends
who came in here with him.
[MACARON] They looked pretty
beat‐up when they were found.
One guy said:
"There's a frickin' huge
labyrinth in there, dude."
[bleh]
[SEIYA] Does that mean they
ended up finding the treasure?
[TIRAMY] If that's true,
we're gonna be rich, mii!
[SEIYA] Don't get too excited.
It's a dead end.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE MOOLAH?!
[waaahhh!!!]
Tiramy, this is embarrassing.
I can't believe I wasted all
this time on that ridiculous
story you guys told me.
Come on, let's go‐
[TIRAMY] Check it out!
I found a secret switch, mii!
[SEIYA] You call that secret?!
[TIRAMY] Now, let's see what
happens when we push it!
No! Wait a second!
[TIRAMY] (shove)
[stone grinding]
[ALL] Whoa!
Moff! Seems legit.
I feel like a badass, ron!
Aw, yeah! That's what
I'm talkin' about, mii!
Shall we go?
[SEIYA] (ah!)
Wait, Sento! Shouldn't we check
the place out before we just‐
[stone grinding]
[SEIYA] (huh?) (ah!)
[ALL]
We locked ourselves iiiiiin!
[MACARON]
We're gonna die in here!
[ALL] (waaahhh!)
[TIRAMY] It was a trap, mii!
[SEIYA] I told you idiots!
[SEIYA] (sigh)
No way to go but forward,
I guess.
[knock on door]
Can we come in?
Mr. Kanie, we were just hoping
we could talk to you
about a new show...
Huh?
[SYLPHY] Woohoooooo!
Miss Isuzu and Mr. Kanie
must've stepped away.
Maybe you should try
texting them real quick.
[hmm...] Let's see here...
[SYLPHY] Ina Bauerrrr!
[phone jingle]
[ISUZU] I'm surprised
we have a signal.
[phone chime]
[MUSE] (ah!)
[SYLPHY] Super Sylphy is at
the top of her game today!
Does that say "hole"?
[SYLPHY]
Go, go, go, go, go, go, goooo!
What kinda weird emoji is that?
[SYLPHY] Skeletooooon!
What the...
[GUARDIAN] (evil laughter)
[ALL] Whoa!
I am the guardian of
this accursed realm.
Come, adventurers, enter the
Forsaken Labyrinth of Doom!
Did he just talk?!
[MACARON] Oh my, ron!
Such a thing defies
scientific possibility, mii!
Oh, yeah, sure! This coming
from the talking pink cat!
[stone grinding]
[ALL] (wah!)
[BOTH] Wow!
[GUARDIAN]
Choose one of these coffins.
You will be granted a weapon
of ultimate power!
Is he seriously just
handing out weapons, mii?!
I hope we don't get
eternally cursed or something.
[hmmm?]
[SEIYA] A shovel?
And I got a stun gun. [crackle]
Check out this huge metal bat!
Molotov cocktails!
That's awesome!
Mine had a chain.
This stuff seems oddly violent
for a family theme park.
[GUARDIAN] Proceed into the
darkness, fearless heroes!
You may go!
[doors creaking]
I feel like something's gonna
jump up out of nowhere.
[MOFFLE]
Don't let your guard down.
[loud click]
[TIRAMY] (hmm?)
What'd I step on?
[MACARON] (hmm?)
[BOTH] (waaahhh!!)
Oh man, that was close!
I thought we were goners, ron!
[TIRAMY] (waaahhh!)
[TIRAMY] Y‐yeah,
I don't wanna be rich after all!
Let's just go home now, mii!
[SEIYA] Go home?! How?!
Calm the moff down.
First, we need to come up
with a survival strategy.
Isuzu!
I'm ready!
[MOFFLE] Tiramy,
we'll take the front!
Macaron, bring up the rear and
keep an eye out for traps.
Isuzu, protect the kid!
[THREE]
Roger that, Captain Moffle!
Do you guys hear
how dumb you sound?
Now, let's get a moff on!
[loud click]
[gulp!]
I think I just moffed up.
[SEIYA] You what?!
[rumbling]
[ALL] Huh?
[THREE] Cliché at 12 o' clock!
[MOFFLE] All units retreat!
[phone jingle]
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[phone chime]
[THREE] (oh...)
[SYLPHY] Whoo, Super
Sylphy takes the lead again!
Like I said, I don't get
her choice of emoji.
[SYLPHY] I'm a luge champion‐
(crash!)
[click]
[BOTH] (waaahhh!)
[ALL] (hyah!)
[waaahhh!!!]
[snick!]
[SEIYA] (ungh!)
[waahh!]
Kanie!
[SEIYA] (argh!)
[ungh!] [oofff!]
[gasp!]
Sento!
ALL] (gasp!)
[OOOWWW!!!]
Sento!
You're more of a jerk
than I thought.
[MOFFLE] Moff!
Let's get outta here!
[SEIYA] (struggling)
[SEIYA] (panting)
They got her...
[MOFFLE]
No time to cry about that.
We have to find a way out of
this crazy place first.
[SEIYA] I know, I just...
Wait, mii!
Sounds like we got company.
[grunts & grumbles]
[SEIYA] What are those things?
They're ABOUT to get
their butts kicked.
Let's moff 'em up!
Why would you
pick a fight with them?!
[hmpf!]
Let the men handle this,
chicken boy.
[grrr]
[growls & slobbering]
[TIRAMY] Here they come!
Eat this!
[ORCS] (ungh!)
NOW, DANCE!
[ORCS] (waahh!!)
[clang!]
[ORC] (ungh...)
sigh]
[MOFFLE] Heh‐heh‐heh...
Let the bloodbath begin!
I'm gonna make you punks beg
for the sweet release of death!
Can we just go?
[ISUZU] (nnnhhh...)
[MACARON] (ugh...)
[gasp]
Where are we?
[MACARON]
Some kind of holding cell.
I need a nice long bath.
[MACARON]
Not till we get out of here.
[sigh]
[MACARON]
Now, how do we open this?
Do you have like a hairpin
or something to‐ [gasp!]
[gunshot]
I've got something much better.
I always liked you, ron.
That's odd.
Why is it so quiet?
You'd think an alarm would
go off or something like that.
[DORNELL] (giggle)
This picture is priceless!
[BOTH] (huh?)
[perverted laughter]
What kind of place is this?
[DORNELL]
Huh? Food's here already?
[huh?!] Dornell‐ron!
You're still alive?!
[hmm?]
[SEIYA] (panting)
[SEIYA] I'm so exhausted...
I can't dig anymore.
[TIRAMY] I'm all out
of Molotov cocktails.
If only there was some chemical
fertilizer lying around,
I could whip up some
sick explosives and wipe
this place out, mii.
[SEIYA] Great, the giant, pink
kitten makes bombs.
[BOTH] (hmm?)
[BOTH] (wah!)
[ORC] (gyah!)
[SEIYA] There's more of them!
[MOFFLE]
Are you moffin' serious?!
[DORNELL] ...and now here I am.
[MACARON] (hmm...)
So, you're telling us no one
ever came here to rescue you?
And you've spent all this
time collecting figures
and watching anime,
even getting them to set up
internet so you could
play games?
(m‐hmm!)
And you've been down here
for ten years.
Uh‐huh!
It's so comfy down here.
Hey, would you mind bringing me
something to snack on?
I'm in the mood for some
potato chips today.
Oh, and some oolong tea
and three cups.
Thanks a bunch!
Listen... Don't you have
a problem with the fact
that everybody in the park
thought you were dead
for the past ten years?
[ISUZU] Why didn't you tell
anyone you were alive?
(hmmm...) At first I just wanted
it to be a long vacation.
But after a while, it was
too awkward to tell anyone.
Plus, that was around the same
time I got hooked on MMOs.
What's an MMO?
[MACARON] (ugh)
[DORNELL]
You know, online games.
For a while there, I was logging
in for like 20 hours every day.
That's pretty disgusting, ron.
But how did you live your life
in solitude for all these years
[DORNELL] (huh...)
without interacting with anyone?
[DORNELL] Well, I play as a
girl, so I'm kinda popular.
[MACARON] I'm not sure how
to respond to that...
[MOLE] Pardon me.
[BOTH] Huh?
I brought you the chips and
oolong tea you asked for.
Oh, perfect, thank you so much!
[BOTH] He's even got a servant?
[running feet]
[ALL] (hyah!)
[ORCS] (roar!)
[ALL] (panting)
I can't believe we almost died
over some stupid treasure!
[WAAHHH!!!]
[rumbling growl]
[SEIYA] A‐A‐A dragon?!
Moff, it's just one thing
after another today.
We're dead, mii!
I am known as Rubrum.
My wisdom surpasses that of man.
Tell me, why have you
disturbed my slumber?
Oh God, what do we do now?!
He's gonna eat us!
Just calm down.
Man up and look him
right in the eye!
If you're so brave,
stop using me as a meat shield!
[ahem] We're sorry for
bothering you, Mr. Rubrum, sir.
I promise you we're not here
to make trouble.
You see, the thing is we
kinda lost our way.
So all we're trying to do is
get back to our friends safely.
[RUBRUM] As I told you,
I surpass human wisdom.
How can you hope
to fool me with lies?
You have only come here
to obtain the hidden treasure!
[SEIYA] No, sir! I'm the
acting manager of this park.
I'm just here to do a
routine inspection of all
the attractions!
[RUBRUM] Ha! I have lived
in this world for eons now,
and my intelligence is
far greater than your own.
You cannot deceive me!
Yeah, yeah, we get it!
You're smart or whatever.
Can we move on now?
Tiramy!
[RUBRUM] You dare insult me?
Then, you will pay for your
impertinence with your lives!
[ORCS] (growls & roars)
[TIRAMY]
We're in trouble now, mii!
[MOFFLE] If I'm goin' down,
I'm takin' all these jokers
down with me!
Wait, I've got an idea.
Hey, Rubrum! You keep telling
us you're more intelligent
than all of mankind,
isn't that right?
Don't make me laugh!
I can tell you're a liar!
[RUBRUM] (angry growl)
What did you say, human?
I'm a hell of a lot
smarter than you are,
you overgrown lizard!
I'd certainly like to
see you prove it.
[SEIYA] You bet!
Ask me any question you want.
But if I get the right answer,
then you have to let us go free.
Deal?
[RUBRUM] Very well.
But if you cannot answer
correctly, you had better
be prepared to face my wrath.
You got it.
Let's go!
Then answer me this,
you pitiful fool of a mortal.
It has to do with
an ancient legend.
[RUBRUM] Back in the olden days,
Illimo the First from the
land of Legnum Sonim...
[RUBRUM] This little whelp
couldn't possibly know the Holy
Grail of Noitomorp Runostargnoc
the Wise.
[RUBRUM] ...still‐
[SEIYA] The Holy Grail of
Noitomorp Runostargnoc the Wise.
What?! B‐but I haven't
even finished asking you
the full question yet.
But I was correct, wasn't I?
Uh, well, uh...
Was I right or not?
[RUBRUM] You were.
[MOFFLE] Moff!
That was absolutely incredible!
How did you know the
answer to that?!
[SEIYA] Ha! Trade secret.
[RUBRUM]
Th‐there must be some mistake!
That question is taken from
the elite Schuvert
Agricultural University's
entrance exam for the
Livestock Alchemy department!
There was no way you
could have known that!
[SEIYA] It's an exam question?
[MOFFLE] Nerd.
Ah, don't make fun of me!
Regardless, I cannot
allow you to leave alive!
You know, he's not that
intimidating anymore.
[MOFFLE] That's a good point!
I feel like I can actually
take this guy now.
[hnngggh!]
[RUBRUM] (ungh!) (ooowww!)
You're tougher than I thought.
Fine!
Stop, Moffle.
[MOFFLE]
Get ready for some pain!
Dragon Slayer Technique!
[SEIYA] I said stop!
[MOFFLE] (ooff!)
What's your problem?!
You're wasting your breath.
[MOFFLE] (hmm?)
I'm really sorry, all right?
I just got a little too
carried away, that's all!
But still, you didn't have to
hit me like that!
I mean, to be fair,
I shouldn't have let myself
get all worked up
just because you're the
first guests I've had
in several years.
[SEIYA] Wait, "guests"?
Yes, you're only the
second group of adventurers
to visit
Rubrum's Chamber of Trials
since this attraction
came into existence.
[ALL] It wasn't real?!
[ISUZU]
Rubrum's telling the truth.
[ALL] (huh?!)
[SEIYA] Sento!
[TIRAMY] I'm so glad
you guys are alive, mii!
[MOFFLE] Hey, wait, that's...
that's Dornell!
Why are you guys so
obsessed with me?
[MOLE] Whew, boy!
[SEIYA] (huh?)
[ALL] (sighs of relief)
[SEIYA] (ah!)
[SEIYA] An attraction
that never opened?
[TARAMO] Let me explain
everything in detail.
[SEIYA] (huh?)
Name's Taramo.
Nice to meet ya!
I happen to be the leader
of the Digerry clan.
[SEIYA] So you're the
one in charge here?
All right, I'm all ears.
But I don't have all day, so
keep it to 20 seconds or less.
O‐kay!
While my people have a great
talent for construction,
we've always been kinda pushed
around by the powers that be.
Just when things were
gettin' rough,
the park authorities agreed to
let us take refuge here.
But we had to make it appear
on paper as an "attraction".
There ya go, with time to spare.
[MOLES] Hurray!
I'm lost.
The Digerry clan was starting
to get a lot of crap
from a bunch of bullies
who call themselves the
Polytia Empire.
From what I understand,
it was supposed to be a secret
that AmaBri helped get the
clan out of trouble with them.
Something suspicious was
happening with money as well.
You mean the park
spent money on this?
[TARAMO] They gave us some
construction funds to live on
at the beginning,
but when that was gone we had to
dip into our assets.
[ISUZU] Assets?
Are you referring to...
Oh yeah, our treasure used to
fill up this entire main hall,
but we spent every
last bit of it.
[ALL] Whaaaat?!
[TIRAMY] That's no fair, mii!
[ISUZU] (sigh)
[MACARON] So we came all the
way down here for nothing
and risked our lives?!
[phone chime]
[ALL] (ah!)
[SYLPHY] Rah, rah, rah! Whoo!
Do you think she's really okay?
[SYLPHY] Bobsled! (crash)
[LATIFAH] I hear you all had
quite the adventure today.
Yeah, I wanted to talk to
you about that actually.
[gasp]
[SEIYA] That's about it.
Oh my goodness,
that's quite a story.
[sigh] To tell you the truth,
well, I...
[TARAMO] Hey!
[LATIFAH] (gasp)
[TARAMO] Miss Manager!
[ALL] (ah!)
[RUMRUM] Whoa, there!
'Scuse me, coming through,
sorry everybody!
Please forgive me, friends.
You see, I wasn't able to fit
through the staff corridor...
[SEIYA]
Did you just fly your giant
dragon self over a public road?!
Evening, Miss Manager.
It's a pleasure to get
to speak with you.
Oh, no, the pleasure's all mine.
[TIRAMY] Kanie, mii!
We need to make an announcement.
Did something bad happen?
We did some digging, and it
turns out the Polytia Empire
fell apart after a
pretty nasty uprising.
Which means the Digerry clan's
got nothing to be afraid of
anymore, mii!
Well, that's convenient,
isn't it?
Really?
Are you sure that's true?!
[MOFFLE] Yup!
So, we're finally free.
In that case, would you please
consider giving all of us a job?
[SEIYA] A job?!
I'd like to be employed
here as well.
I promise I'll do my VERY best
to scare the visitors!
[LATIFAH]
(mmm...) Interesting...
What do you say to that,
Sir Kanie?
Sure, I can put
you guys to work.
[TARAMO] Gosh, you mean it?
[SEIYA] Yeah, but fair warning,
I'm gonna work you to
the bone every day.
[ALL] Hurray! Way to go!
But, Kanie,
what'll we do about the money?
Oh! Just leave everything
to yours truly, ron.
Did they really build that
thing overnight?!
[GUY] (hmm...)
Yep, that's the total.
(huh?)
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Come back! (waahh!) (sobbing)
[ISUZU]
Selling off Dornell's collection
ought to get us through
the month at least.
[SEIYA] Good.
But that doesn't exactly take
care of our biggest problem.
What are you going to do now?
[SEIYA] (sigh)
[TIRAMY & MACARON] (snickering)
[TIRAMY]
I got the goods right here, mii!
Sweet, I can't wait
to try these babies out!
This is gonna be killer...
[BOTH] (crazed laughing)
[ISUZU & SEIYA] Time for
the attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU] Today's feature
is Planet Dinosaur,
a prehistoric adventure where
dinosaurs still roam the Earth.
I hear Triken makes an
appearance here sometimes.
[SEIYA] Oh, I thought he
was just Chief of Sales.
[ISUZU] Kids and parents alike
can't get enough of this
educational thrill ride
from the Triassic to the
Cretaceous Period.
[SEIYA] I see. Is there like a
grand finale, too?
[ISUZU] Yes, they go extinct.
[SEIYA] That's not fun at all!