[ISUZU]
Amagi Transport says
they can add more buses.
[ISUZU]
And as for the sports stadium...
I haven't gotten
a definite response yet.
[SEIYA]
Sounds good... Keep it up.
[ISUZU]
I did get an answer from Moll
Mart about the‐
...other thing.
[ISUZU]
Kanie?
[SEIYA]
Sorry... I feel kinda dizzy...
[ISUZU]
(scared) Kanie! What's wrong?!
[MUSE]
Mr. Kanie passed out?!
[KOBORY]
What'd the doctor say?
[ISUZU]
Probably just exhaustion
mixed with a cold.
[MUSE]
Good, that's not too serious.
[KOBORY] We'd be in trouble if
he had to go to the hospital.
[SYLPHY] Nice poker face!
[SYLPHY] I'm stuck...
[MUSE]
I wonder if we can help him.
I know! I could keep him
hydrated with my water spells!
[SALAMA]
And I'll keep him warm with my
fire.
[KOBORY]
And I'll bury him
to leech out the poison.
[SALAMA] I don't think that'll
work for a cold...
[SYLPHY] Whoa! I'm not worthy!
[LATIFAH]
I'm sorry, I won't let you.
[SEIYA]
But it's just a little cold.
The paperwork's piling up‐
[LATIFAH]
Absolutely not‐
I command you to remain at home
until you've made a complete
recovery.
[SEIYA]
Let me guess‐ you're not gonna
let me go to school either.
[LATIFAH]
Sir Kanie.
Do not underestimate
the importance of your health.
[SEIYA]
(watching)
I hope you feel better soon...
Now get some rest.
[SEIYA]
Well that's great...
[ISUZU]
How are you feeling, Kanie?
[SEIYA]
Hey Sento.
Look, could you please tell
that princess of yours
not to worry so much?
[SEIYA]
Hold on... What's that
weird thing on your head?
[ISUZU]
Just ignore it.
[SEIYA]
I've missed a lot of
school days already.
I can't afford to take
any more ti‐
[SEIYA]
S‐Sento?!
Hey! (nervous)
[ISUZU]
I want to be more than
just your secretary‐ Kanie...
[SEIYA]
Whoa, I think this summer heat's
getting to your head!
[ISUZU] Don't pull away.
[SEIYA] (extended awkwardness)
[ISUZU]
I need to tell you...
I... I want you...
[TIRAMY]
Just kidding‐ it was me
all along mii!
[MACARON]
You sucker‐ron!
[SEIYA]
What the...?
[TIRAMY]
(chortling)
[SEIYA]
How did you...
[TIRAMY/MACARON]
(explode into laughter)
[TIRAMY]
It's a magic Isuzu costume!
[MACARON]
Yeah, we modified it from
the ones they use in the
Diggery Clan‐ron!
[SEIYA]
That's messed up.
[TIRAMY]
Well at least now you don't have
to worry
about missing your classes‐mii!
[SEIYA]
I can't believe what
I'm hearing.
You guys want to make
a costume of me and go to my‐
[MACARON]
Mhm! That's right‐ we wanna go
to school in your place!
[TIRAMY]
It's a pretty complete
prototype.
Unfortunately‐ we weren't
able to get an exact reference
for the parts underneath
the clothes...
so we used our
imaginations‐mii!
[MACARON/TIRAMY]
(realize)
[TIRAMY]
Oh... when'd you get here Isuzu?
[MACARON/TIRAMY]
(trembling)
[MOFFLE]
Moff... I don't think
it's a bad idea.
I mean‐ what else
are you gonna do?
It's not like you have
any friends.
[SEIYA] (offended)
[MOFFLE]
It'll be fine
if they keep quiet.
[SEIYA]
(annoyed) (stunned) Ugh...
[ISUZU]
Then it's settled.
[GIRL]
Oh, I know. What about
spaghetti?
[ISUZU]
What an amazing item...
It's exactly like the original.
(incoming stampede)
[SEIYA]
(gasp)
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
Wahoo! Heh heh!
[BRAT A]
Jackpot!
I smell a girl!
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
(menacing)
(MENACING)
[SEIYA]
(gulp)
[BRAT C]
False alarm.
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
(cackling)
[SEIYA]
(relieved)
[SHIINA]
K... Kanie?
[SEIYA]
(startled)
[SHIINA]
Good morning, sir!
I heard you passed out from a
cold recently and um...
Wait. what's that?
[SEIYA] (like Isuzu) G‐good
morning, Miss Chujo...
It's nothing.
[SHIINA]
What?
Ah, I mean,
good morning, Chujo...
And yeah, I'm not sick anymore.
Oh...
Anyway do I look nice
and handsome today?
[SHIINA]
I'm not sure how to respond
to that...
But you seem like you're in a
good mood!
[SEIYA] You think so?
[SHIINA] Yeah...
I mean, most of the time
you just kind of ignore me.
[SHIINA]
So I... I'm uh... I'm happy, I
guess!(turn away)
[ISUZU]
Goodness...
Kanie must really
treat that girl poorly.
[SEIYA]
Hm?
(reading)
"I've liked you ever
since my first year.
No matter what people
say about you,
I can tell you're
a really nice person.
If it isn't too much trouble,
I'd like you to meet me
behind the gymnasium
after school this afternoon.
Please give me the chance to
tell you how I feel"?!
[TEACHER]
(drones on lesson under)
[ISUZU]
What should I do?
I thought of texting Kanie
to see what he thinks about it,
but he's still resting
and I'd hate to bother him.
[TEACHER]
This concept is sure to be on
your test.
[SEIYA]
It was a mistake?
[KANAE]
Yeah, I could've sworn that
shoebox
belonged to Kimura
from class 2‐5.
So I never meant for that love
letter to go to you.
Um... what's that on your head?
[SEIYA]
Just ignore it.
Uh, so what you're saying is
you're not in love with Kanie...
I mean, so I'm not the guy
you're in love with huh?
[KANAE]
No... I guess you're upset...
I really am sorry about this!
[SEIYA] It's quite alright.
[KANAE] Huh?
[SEIYA]
Everyone makes mistakes
sometimes.
You didn't sign the letter,
so you could've just run away
when you realized what happened,
but you went out of your way
to apologize and
set things right.
That was very professional.
[KANAE]
Does that mean you forgive me?
There's nothing to forgive
you for...
Thanks for being considerate.
[KANAE]
(happy) Wow, thank you so much,
Kanie.
When I realized what I had done,
I was so afraid you were going
to yell at me or something.
[SEIYA]
It's fine... In fact...
I wish you the best in all your
endeavors, Miss Kanae Tsuchida.
[KANAE]
You know... I'm kind of happy
I misplaced that letter.
[SEIYA]
(confused)
Well, goodbye for now!
[SEIYA]
"For now"?
[MACARON]
So you didn't have any
major issues?
[ISUZU]
No, there was nothing worth
reporting...
I hope you'll be as
successful tomorrow.
[MACARON]
Ah high school...
so many memories‐ron!
I don't suppose you've ever
heard of Dokidoki Melody High
School in Maple Land?
It's super‐famous for being full
of troublemakers‐ron.
[ISUZU]
Yes, I'm always hearing about
violent incidents.
[MACARON]
I was top sheep back in the day.
Got expelled halfway through,
though.
We had a little scrap with some
guys from another school
so they gave me the boot‐
[ISUZU] I'm not interested.
[MACARON] Oh. Well.
[ISUZU]
Just try not to cause any
problems.
[MACARON]
Don't worry about me.
I can blend right in
with those youngsters‐ron.
[SEIYA]
(relaxing)
[TEACHER]
Ah... Listen, son...
You can't do that in class...
and what's that on your head?
[SEIYA]
Just ignore it and focus on
doing your job, old man.
[TEACHER]
Wh... what did you say?!
[SEIYA]
You're such a drag‐ron!
[TEACHER]
(startled)
S‐stay back!
I don't want to fi‐(speechless)
[SEIYA]
Hey teach...
I'm not feelin' so good,
so I'm gonna go see
the nurse now.
See ya.
[TEACHER]
Huh?
[SHIINA]
Um, is that you, Mr. Kanie?
[SEIYA]
Hm? Oh... it's you‐ron.
[SHIINA]
You‐ron? I don't‐
[SEIYA]
I forgot you were my
classmate‐ron.
[SHIINA]
What?
[SEIYA]
Lunchtime already, huh?
Man, this place is so boring
I can't even smoke a cigarette.
I don't know how much I can take
before I snap.
[SHIINA]
Did you say "snap"?
[SEIYA]
Hey, wanna skip class with me?
I'm gonna go play some
pachinko later.
[SHIINA]
(shock)
N‐no thanks, I'm good, bye!
Jeez, was it something I said?
[KIMURA]
What do you mean, mistake?
Terano told me you were planning
to give me a letter...
What happened to that?
[KANAE]
I was going to...
but now I can't figure out
my true feelings.
[KANAE]
I'm having trouble deciding if
that's what I really want to do.
[KIMURA]
But how can you say that?!
If you had asked me out,
I would've said yes in a
heartbeat!
[KANAE]
I know, but things have
changed...
[MACARON]
They could use some love advice
from yours truly‐ron.
[SEIYA]
Take it easy there, son.
[KANAE/KIMURA]
(surprised)
[KANAE]
Kanie?!
[KIMURA]
Were you spying on us?!
[SEIYA]
Oh, don't have a cow, ron.
[KIMURA]
"Ron"?
[SEIYA]
I mean, uh...(ahem)
Take it from me kid,
the harder you chase after
a lady the faster she runs away.
You just gotta be cool...
Better to step aside
and let her collect her
thoughts for a while
than make an ass of
yourself‐ron... Understand?
[KIMURA]
Who asked you?!
And what's that?!
[SEIYA]
Just ignore it.
[KIMURA]
I don't need advice from
the guy who got Tsuchida's
love letter by mistake!
[SEIYA]
Huh?!
[KIMURA]
She had her eye on me
in the first place,
and then THIS had
to happen!
You're the last person
I want to talk to about this,
you got that?!
[SEIYA]
Wait a sec...
Did you say she gave
ME a letter?
[KANAE]
Y‐yes.
I wasn't trying to make
you guys fight over me
or anything bad like that...
but you were just so
nice to me...
and now I can't decide
who I like!
I don't remember any of this
from the report.
[KIMURA] (ggh!)
[SEIYA] Maybe it happened a
while ago...
Why are you trying to pretend
like you don't remember?!
What, are you making fun of me?!
[SEIYA]
Don't be silly.
I would never make
fun of you, buddy‐ron.
[KIMURA]
It sure as heck sounds
like you are to me!
I'm heartbroken... You jerk...
You're gonna pay!
[MACARON]
Too slow! I could easily
beat this guy‐ggh!
[KIMURA]
(look)Huh?
Huh... That was a pretty
good punch,
but it's still kinda flimsy
if you ask me.
You're never gonna knock out the
king of Doki‐Melo High with an
arm like that.
[KIMURA]
Uh, Kanie...
[SEIYA]
What's up?
Your head is sort of uh...
[SEIYA]
Hm? Oh jeez, you're right.
[KIMURA]
(horrified)
[SEIYA]
Anyway, what was I
just talking about?
[KIMURA]
(scream)
[SEIYA]
See ya...
[KANAE]
Um, are you sure you're okay?
[SEIYA]
Oh, yeah I'm alright...
Just really flexible, is all.
[KANAE]
I‐I guess that makes sense...
Good to hear.
[MACARON]
This girl's got serious issues
if she's willing to
believe that.
[KANAE]
I'm sorry, Kanie.
You didn't do anything to
deserve that.
Don't sweat it...
Everybody makes mistakes,
don't they?
[KANAE]
But I...
Look honey‐ron,
I learned a lot about this kinda
thing from being divorced...
[KANAE]
D... divorced?!
[SEIYA]
It's always better
if you can have
a third party
for your arguments.
If it's just the two of you
fighting about it,
you tend to get emotional and
not solve anything.
[KANAE]
Oh...
[SEIYA] Find a friend
both of you trust
and discuss everything over
coffee or something like that.
You're less likely
to lose your cool
in front of a friend. Bye!
[KANAE] One more thing, Kanie!
[SEIYA] Hm?
That could've been really bad if
you hadn't stepped in like that.
Thank you so much!
Don't bow... It makes
you look weak
and you're a lot stronger
than that.
[KANAE]
(gasp) Right!
[ISUZU]
You didn't have any
catastrophes then?
Well, I did have a few hiccups
here and there,
but I don't think it was
anything worth getting
concerned about.
[TIRAMY]
Tomorrow's my turn!
This really takes me back
to my days
at Wakuwaku Garden
High School‐mii!
[MACARON]
Oh wow, Tiramy‐ron, I had no
idea
you went to such a
competitive high school!
[ISUZU]
If I remember correctly,
that school had some kind of
explosion years ago.
Yeah that may or may not
have been me‐mii.
[TIRAMY] I was in the science
club back then,
[SALAMA] So how's the boss?
[TIRAMY] I was in the science
club back then,
[MUSE] Princess won't let him
come back to work.
[TIRAMY] But I didn't know
how strong it was,
[SALAMA/MUSE/KOBORY] Uhh...
and it sorta blew the whole
building to kingdom come.
I felt pretty bad about it
when it happened‐(ggh!)
[ISUZU]
It doesn't sound like you felt
bad enough.
[MACARON]
That's an interesting story,
Tiramy.
[ISUZU]
Don't encourage him. You'd
better hope you don't blow up
Kanie's school or else.
[TIRAMY]
Don't worry, I know
exactly how to think like
a high school boy‐mii!
[TIRAMY]
Hot damn!
This place is just crawling with
cute girls in miniskirts!
[SEIYA]
Ahhh, how'm I gonna behave
myself‐mii?
[KANAE]
Um, Kanie?
[SEIYA]
Mii?
[KANAE]
Um...
I was hoping I could have
a little chat with you.
[KANAE]
Do you mind?
[SEIYA]
Yes please!
[KANAE]
S‐sure...
[TIRAMY]
YES! Yes yes yes yes YES!
Attaboy, Kanie!
I never knew you were friends
with such a gorgeous babe!
I'm gonna bag her for sure‐mii!
[SEIYA]
Let me ask you something.
[KANAE]
Yes?
[SEIYA]
Your name... what is it?
[KANAE]
(gasp)
My name's Kanae Tsuchida...
[KANAE]
How could you forget already?
[SEIYA]
Aw, I didn't forget it!
I just like to hear you say it
with your sexy voice‐mii.
[KANAE]
"Mii"?
[SEIYA]
Yeah you. Now say it again...
What's your name?
[KANAE]
Kanae... Tsuchida.
[SEIYA]
Yeah... that was beautiful...
I wanna hear it again!
[KANAE]
Stop teasing me, Kanie!
[SEIYA]
(giggle) No way... How could I
possibly stop teasing you
when you're just so deliciously
cute‐mii?
[KANAE]
(surprised)
Come on... Follow mii.
[KANAE]
The stairway?
[SEIYA]
Hehehe...
I wanna go someplace quiet
so I can tease you more.
[KANAE]
Huh?
[SEIYA]
No need to be scared‐mii...
I'll hold your hand every step
of the way, okay?
[KANAE]
(shy)
[TIRAMY]
Damn, that was easy, mii!
This costume is gonna come in
real handy from now on!
[SHIINA]
Mr. Kanie?
[SEIYA]
Mii?
Oh... Hey Shiina.
[SHIINA]
Um, who is she?
Come on, do I really have to
spell it out for you‐mii?
Me and this cutie are about to
get busy!
[KANAE]
K‐Kanie!
[SEIYA]
Trust mii.
(blow)
[KANAE]
(flustered)
Sorry babe...
You're just gonna have to wait
in line for the next ti‐Mii!
That's gross! How can you talk
like that?!
You'll be sorry.
I'm telling Miss Sento!
[SEIYA]
Shiina's acting weird today‐mii.
[KANAE]
Kanie, how do you know
that girl?
[SEIYA]
She's just some chick
I work with‐mii.
Anyway, I think we're alone now
so why don't you‐
[SEIYA]
What now‐mii?
[KANAE]
I don't know what to think of
you saying "mii"
every 10
seconds like that, Kanie.
[SEIYA]
Who cares‐mii?...
Now come over here
and let me show you the
meaning of pleasure‐mii!
[KANAE]
What kind of relationship
do you have with her?
Plus, isn't Sento that quiet
girl who's been really
friendly with you lately?
Does that make me
girlfriend number 3?
[SEIYA]
Listen baby, the whole thing's
pretty complicated, alright?
[KANAE]
You've been acting really weird
these past couple of days...
I'm starting to get the idea
you mess around with girls'
hearts all the time.
And I just thought you were more
trustworthy than that.
[SEIYA]
I AM trustworthy! I promise I can
be faithful‐mii!
[KANAE]
Okay... Then what's my name?
[SEIYA]
Ah...
Uh...
It's uh... Sanae!
[KANAE]
I'm going home.
[SEIYA]
(sob)But I was so close...
Mii...
[ISUZU]
Nothing happened at all?
You're sure?
Something almost happened,
but rest assured,
absolutely nothing happened.
[ISUZU]
Well that's good.
You're next, Lord Moffle.
[MOFFLE]
High school...
That sure brings back memories.
I went to a strict
boarding school
called Fuwafuwa
Military Academy.
[MOFFLE]
The upperclassmen were all so‐
[ISUZU] I've heard enough.
[MOFFLE] Moff?
Just get through it
with no trouble.
[SEIYA]
What the moff is going on?
[ISUZU]
I don't know. They just asked us
to meet them here.
[TERANO]
Kanie and Sento...
I heard one of my classmates
got her feelings hurt
by you two jerks.
And what's that weird thing
on your head?
Moff‐ just ignore it...
Anyway, I don't understand
what you're mad about‐
[TERANO]
Don't play dumb!
[KANAE]
It's okay Terano,
it really doesn't
bother me that much.
[YAMAMOTO]
Doesn't bother you?
I thought you said this guy
tried to put the moves on you
in the stairwell yesterday!
[SASAKI]
That Sento girl and
some first‐year named Chujo
are both Kanie's girlfriends.
They worked together
to break your heart!
[KANAE]
But I... but I never said that!
[TERANO]
But that's pretty much what
happened.
[ISUZU]
That's ridiculous! I swear upon
the Goddess Libra that
Kanie and I have done no such
thing to this girl!
And you expect me to believe
that? Besides, who's Libra?
[ISUZU]
If you wish to behold
the wrath of Libra,
then I'll show it to you.
[TERANO]
What are you doing?
[SEIYA] Hold it‐moff.
[ISUZU] Are you sure?
[TERANO]
What's with the "moff" thing?
[SEIYA] Let me handle this.
[TERANO] Whatever, I don't care.
just hurry up and apologize to
Kanae. right now!
[SEIYA] I'm sorry.
[TERANO] (shocked)
[MOFFLE]
Eh, moff, who cares about
the kid's pride, anyway?
[TERANO]
No way. I want you to grovel!
[SEIYA]
Okay... how's this?
[TERANO]
Too easy!
Where's your pride?
Don't you dare talk to her
ever again!
[SEIYA]
As moff as my witness.
From the bottom of my heart,
I really do apologize.
[KANAE]
No... wait...
[TERANO]
I'm starting to think
he's making fun of us.
[SEIYA]
No, I honestly feel bad
about it.
[TERANO]
Yeah right. you're just saying
whatever you have to say!
You obviously don't care
about this poor girl's
feelings for you!
[TERANO]
I mean nothing you've said
or done has had a shred of
sincerity to it!
It's like you knocked it off
from a TV show!
[SEIYA] You...
[SASAKI] (hm?)
[YAMAMOTO] (huh?)
You just said the worst
possible thing.
[TERANO]
Huh?
[ISUZU]
Hearing the word "knock‐off"
is extremely
problematic for him.
I have had enough of
you arrogant bitches
and your bullshit!
[TERANO/SASAKI/YAMAMOTO]
(stunned)
Running your mouths
about love and sincerity...
You can't just throw those words
around like they're nothing!
You're a bunch of kids!
Don't make me laugh.
you three don't know the first
moffin' thing about love!
[ISUZU]
Please don't get upset,
Lord Moffle.
[SEIYA]
You date some boy
you barely know,
you think you're in love,
then you complain about
heartbreak afterwards?!
You think life's that easy?!
[SEIYA]
What, does it make you feel cool
to pretend to be angry for
your friend's sake,
is that it?
You're full of it!
[TERANO/YAMAMOTO/SASAKI]
(gasp)
[TERANO]
(stunned)Whoa!
[SEIYA]
When the pain is bad enough
to make you wish
you were dead...
THAT... THAT'S what love is!
Wait 'til the woman you've
loved for over ten years
gets married to some
bastard you hate!
You can't even imagine the agony
I felt that day!
[SEIYA]
And then ten years later,
she comes and asks me to take
care of her daughter?
Do you know how that feels?!
[ISUZU] (surprised)
[SEIYA] No! Because you're
children!
[ISUZU]
Wait a minute sir.
Is this in reference to
Princess Latifah's mother?
[SEIYA]
Shut the moff up,
it's hypothetical!
[TERANO]
What's his problem?!
[SASAKI]
Yeah. he's really creeping
me out.
[YAMAMOTO]
And what does "moff" mean?
[KIMURA]
Stop it, guys!
[SASAKI/YAMAMOTO/TERANO]
(surprised)
[KANAE]
Kimura!
[KIMURA]
I'm sorry...
The only reason Kanie acted
like that was for my sake!
[ALL]
Huh?!
[KIMURA]
He said all those crazy things
and acted like a scumbag
on purpose
to make Tsuchida hate his guts!
That way maybe she'd
want to be with me instead!
[KIMURA]
Right, Kanie?
[SEIYA]
I what...? Uhhh, yeah...
[KIMURA]
When I asked Kanie for advice
about how to patch everything up
with Tsuchida...
he had a plan...
He said the only way to get
things back to normal
was to make her not
like him anymore.
I know this mess ended up making
me look bad too...
But I swear I'll try really hard
to be the best guy for you.
[KIMURA]
So do you think maybe
you could give me a chance?
[KANAE]
O‐okay... If you're sure that's
what you want too.
[TERANO]
Well then if the two of you
don't have anything left to be
upset over...
I guess I have nothing to say.
[KIMURA]
Awesome!...
Thank you for understanding!
[KIMURA]
It's nice to have friends,
huh?(big laughter)
[SEIYA] (unzipping)
Thanks for the
heads‐up, Chujo...
It all worked out,
thanks to you.
[SHIINA]
Sure... I knew something weird
must be going on...
It's a good thing I was able to
get in contact with you.
[SEIYA]
I appreciate it.
Hopefully I can figure out a way
to explain all this
to Kimura later.
[SHIINA]
I'm surprised you didn't get mad
at Mr. Moffle and the other two.
You almost made a lot of enemies
because of this mess.
[SEIYA]
Nah... I'm not mad...
Either way, those idiots only
did it
because they wanted to
help me out.
[SEIYA]
How could I be mad at that?
[SHIINA]
(smile)
[SEIYA]
What?
[SHIINA]
Oh it's nothing.
I was just thinking
how you reacted the way
I expected you would.
[SEIYA]
Huh?
It's no big deal...
I gotta go!
[SEIYA]
Sento. you made it.
[LATIFAH]
(happy)
It's good to see that you're
back on the job...
I take it you've fully
recovered then.
[LATIFAH]
Look at this, Lady Isuzu...
Sir Kanie is very
peculiar!(giggle)
[ISUZU]
Did something happen?
[LATIFAH]
Just look at the way
he tries his best to preserve
the strawberry on top
until the last possible moment!
[SEIYA]
(surprised)What? is that weird?
You appear to be healthy enough
to return to school tomorrow.
Oh yeah. I'm perfectly fine
now...
Sorry for the trouble. Sento.
[ISUZU]
No... I probably wasn't of very
much help to you in the end.
In fact, I may have caused YOU
trouble.
Well, you can fill me in
later... Are you hungry?
[LATIFAH]
Yes, we have croquettes!
[ISUZU]
Thank you.
[LATIFAH]
Speaking of which,
I've thought of a
new croquette recipe!
[LATIFAH]
If I add sugar to the batter...
they'll be even more appealing
to visitors with a sweet tooth
won't they?
[SEIYA]
Sounds good... I think the
Maple Kitchen
could benefit from
a new menu item.
[LATIFAH]
Then would it be alright if you
sampled the new recipe to make
sure it's perfect
before we serve it to the
guests?
[SEIYA]
Oh I get it.
So I'm a guinea pig now.
[LATIFAH] Oh no...!
I didn't mean it that way!
[SEIYA]
(laugh) It's fine.
[LATIFAH]
Then I'll go ahead and make a
few first thing in the morning.
[SEIYA]
Can't wait to try 'em.
[LATIFAH]
Perfect!
I'm sure you'll like them.
[MUSE]
(determined)
(exert) Haaa! Agghh!
[MUSE]
It's not good enough!
[ISUZU/SEIYA]
Time for the
attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU]
Today's feature is Save the
Earth.
It's a fun‐filled presentation
about Earth science.
[SEIYA]
Oh okay, so it's like a
documentary type thing?
[ISUZU]
Sort of. The audience
experiences a lengthy lecture
from Future the globe
about the many ways
in which humanity destroys
our precious planet.
[SEIYA]
That doesn't sound fun at all.
[ISUZU]
And then after the show,
he demands a 2,000 yen donation
from each visitor.
[SEIYA]
We should shut that down!