[ISUZU]
(gasp)
[SEIYA]
[ISUZU]
What?
But we made sure...
[SEIYA]
It's the ticket
utilization rate.
[ISUZU]
Utilization?
[SEIYA]
I was expecting a couple
of the tickets they sold
to end up being no‐shows...
but I didn't think
the number would be so high!
[SEIYA]
I miscalculated! Damn it!
[TRIKEN]
We'll never get 252 people
by 9 o'clock!
[TRIKEN]
Princess...
I think this may be the end!
[LATIFAH]
(sad)
[Girls]
Please help!
[SALAMA]
C'mon... we're not
asking for much here!
Pretty please?
[MUSE]
All you have to do is walk
through the gate real quick!
[KOBORY]
[SALAMA]
It'll only take a second!
[JAW]
We beseech you, sir!
[FUTURE]
You'll be doing
our world a service!
How about you ladies?
Would you and your little ones
please come visit AmaBri
for just a quick second?
[MOTHER A]
Sorry... we're about
to be late for dinner!
[FUTURE] It won't take long!
[JAW] WE'RE DESPERATE!
[MOTHER A]
Sorry!
[FUTURE]
(worried)
[SEIYA]
Yes, immediately.
We're inviting you to
Amagi Brilliant Park.
Absolutely free!
[SEIYA]
Yes... yes...
[ISUZU]
That's right sir...
it won't cost you anything.
[ASHE]
Of course not...
That's not my intention.
[SEIYA] I see...
[ISUZU] Oh.
[SEIYA]
Sorry to bother you then.
No good.
[ISUZU]
I got turned down again.
[ASHE]
No luck here either.
Wanipee and the girls
are advertising at the station
right now, but...
[EIKO] Please come visit AmaBri!
[BIINO] Free today only!
[SHIINA] We really need your
help, ok?!
[SEIYA]
(nervous) There's gotta be
something we can do!
[REALTOR A]
Come on now!
Don't you kids think
it's about time
for you to
throw in the towel?
[ISUZU/SEIYA/ASHE]
(speechless)
(all surprised)
[MOFFLE]
It's not over yet!
We've still got
a moffin' chance at this!
Let's fight 'til the end!
[SEIYA]
But...
[MOFFLE]
Hey Takami,
sorry to call you at work.
Yeah it's me. Listen.
Could you bring every
single customer you have
over to AmaBri right now?
It's really important.
[SEIYA]
Huh? Hey!
[MOFFLE]
Tell 'em I'll pay their tabs
if they come.
We came up short on visitors.
I'll never ask you
for moffin' else!
Uh‐huh...
Thanks a lot... See ya.
Don't just stand there!
Start calling!
Everyone you know!
[ALL]
(surprised, into search)
You're serious?
Cold‐calling?
[MACARON]
Hey... Pachinko Parlor?
[TIRAMY]
Shizue? Is that you‐mii?
[MUSE]
Hello Grandma‐this is Muse.
[KOBORY]
Sorry to bother you.
Is the con over yet?
[SALAMA]
Most people scroll right past
stuff like this, but... eh.
[SYLPHY]
Tally ho!
[ASHE]
Hello there.
I know it's been a while,
but I actually have a bit
of a favor to ask of you.
[SEIYA]
It's 252 people...
I highly doubt this'll
make enough difference.
Sento, you're in on this too?
[ISUZU]
I'm telling the cast
to help out.
[WRENCH]
Hey buddy, long time no see.
There's a little somethin'
I need from ya...
[TARAMO]
Good evening!
No, I don't need to order
supplies today.
[GENJURO]
Thank you very much!
I do appreciate your support.
[IRONBEARD]
Arr, if ye refuse
it's the gallows fer ya!
[JACK]
Come on, pops! I'm only askin'
for two or three head!
[DORNELL]
Yeah, I'll take a medium
Margherita pizza.
Oh and make sure you bring it
through the main gate please.
[FUTURE]
Ecological emergency... mhm.
[GUY A]
Hello? Hellooo?
[SEIYA]
(inhale, exhale)
(annoyed)
[SEIYA]
(shudder) Fine, I'll do it!
Uh... hey...
is this Terano? It's Kanie.
I was wondering if...
What? No, it's not that.
Listen. I still don't really
understand what happened but...
I'm sorry.
A‐anyway.
I need to ask a favor of you
and it has to be done
right NOW, okay?
[MOFFLE]
Moff!
[TAKAMI]
(smile)
[MOFFLE]
Takami!
Hey. sorry it took us so long!
[MOFFLE]
Sorry to put you out.
[TAKAMI]
Don't mention it.
I could never say no
to a regular in trouble!
[MACARON]
Look! It's them‐ron!
[MANAGER]
What's up?
[TIRAMY]
Who are they‐mii?
They work at my favorite
pachinko place!
[Wives]
(rage)
[MOFFLE]
What the moff is this?
[TIRAMY]
Heh. I told all their husbands
they were cheating on 'em.
[ALL]
(stunned)
[MOFFLE]
You really went all out...
[TIRAMY]
Oh no. This isn't
the half of it‐mii!
[HUSBAND A]
That bastard messed
with my wife!
[TIRAMY]
See? Double the numbers‐mii!
(suffering under)
[CHIBA]
Look mommy.
They're having
a grownup discussion!
[CHIBA'S MOM]
Shush. Just pretend
you don't see anything.
[GRANDMA]
(smile)
[MUSE]
That's my grandma!
[GRANDMA]
Sorry dear...
none of my friends
could make it.
Mm‐mm... I'm just glad
you're here, Grandma!
[WOMAN A]
Gang's all here, Salama!
[SALAMA]
Oh wow! my followers!
[WOMAN B]
Sorry we're late, Kobory.
[KOBORY]
You brought the whole club!
[Fanboys]
Shirukooooo!
[SEIYA/ISUZU/MOFFLE]
Huh?!
[FANBOY B]
I have to see her!
[SYLPHY]
Shiruko is taking the stage!
[MOFFLE]
Do I wanna know?
[MACARON]
Apparently she's an
internet celebrity‐ron.
[MOFFLE]
A million hits?!
[SEIYA]
(surprised looking)
[MOFFLE]
We just need 8 more people.
We might make it!
[TERANO]
Kanie!
Okay we're here, now what?
[SEIYA]
Terano!
[TERANO]
I‐I'm sorry.
I could only get
so many people to come.
[SEIYA]
No... this is great!
[TERANO]
What the heck kinda
goofy outfits are those?
[ISUZU]
Don't worry about that.
[TERANO]
(yanked)
[MOFFLE]
Moff! Only three more!
[ISUZU]
(troubled)
[MOFFLE]
What is it?
[ISUZU]
They were the last people...
That's everyone we contacted.
[SEIYA]
(nervous)(angry)
I don't have anyone
else to call!
Neither do I!
[SYLPHY]
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN PLEASE‐
[SALAMA] I'll try posting again!
[KOBORY]
But we can't lose now!
[MUSE]
Somebody please!
[WANIPEE]
No, it's all over...!
I'm gonna disappear forever!
(sobbing)
Moff!
[ISUZU]
Just three more!
Someone! Anyone!
[SEIYA]
Again... I failed her again!
(angry)
[BRAT B]
Mommy, I'm tired...
[MOTHER A]
We'll be home soon, okay?
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
Huh?
IT'S A GIRLLLL!
[ISUZU]
(look up)
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
Wahoo!
[ISUZU]
(gasp) (grabbed)
[MOFFLE/SEIYA]
Don't you move.
[ISUZU]
(gasp)
(maniacal running)
[BRAT C]
Hah!
[BRAT A]
Yahoo!
[BRAT B]
Yeahhh!
(shrieking laughter)
[SEIYA]
We... we won...
[MOFFLE]
Moffin' barely... (excited)
500,000! The park is saved!
[MACARON] Nice goin'‐ron!
[TIRAMY] That was awesome‐mii!
[SYLPHY] (giggles)
[KOBORY] (dizzy)
[SALAMA/MUSE]
(jumping excitement)
[NICK/FUTURE] (laughter)
[WANIPEE] (happy sobs)
[OKURO]
(victory scream)
[ALL]
(celebrating)
[EIKO/BIINO/SHIINA]
(giggle)(look)
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
(tantrum)
[ISUZU]
(suffering)
[REALTOR A]
Hmph...
[SEIYA]
Ha... ha ha... haaahhhh...
[MOFFLE]
All tuckered out?
[SEIYA]
(surprised) No I'm not...
[MOFFLE]
Seiya.
[SEIYA]
(shocked)
[MOFFLE]
I gotta admit...
We have you to thank
for saving us.
[SEIYA]
(speechless)
[MUSE/KOBORY]
Mr. Kanie!
[JAW]
Thankyouthankyouthankyou!
[SYLPHY/SALAMA]
(happy)
[MACARON/TIRAMY]
(tackle)
It's... it's a miracle!
I'm practically hunched over
in tears... (sob)
[SEIYA]
Hey! get off of me
ya bunch of goofballs!
you're heavier than you think!
[LATIFAH]
Sir Kanie... Everyone...!
Thank you...
Thank you so much
for all you've done!
[FUTURE]
Alright!
Here's to pulling together
to save the earth from
total destruction! Cheers!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[OKURO/JACK]
(laughing)
[TRIKEN]
Excuse me sirs!
[SEIYA]
Everything's settled.
Yes! the park will be open
tomorrow as normal.
[SEIYA]
Now, about selling the land...
Oh that's excellent,
thank you so much!
[ASHE/ISUZU]
(happy)
[SEIYA]
We'll send someone over
in a few days.
[MOFFLE]
Okay, say moff!
[EIKO/BIINO/SHIINA]
Moff!
[EIKO/BIINO]
Thank you so much,
Princess Latifah!
[LATIFAH]
[SHIINA]
Th‐thank you for t‐taking it,
M‐Mr. Moffle!
[MOFFLE]
Moff, no trouble at all.
[EIKO/BIINO/SHIINA]
We'll see you later!
[SEIYA]
Can I get everyone's attention?
We have today's guest count.
Turns out we had 54976 people.
[MUSE]
(happy)
As I told everybody
when this whole thing started,
I'll be stepping down as manager
from this day forward.
[ALL]
Huh?
I remember I was so shocked when
I saw how bad this place was.
Well it's still pretty bad!
[ALL]
(laughter)
[SEIYA]
Seriously, you losers
had better be glad I'm a genius!
[MACARON]
What a stuck‐up jerk‐ron!
[WRENCH]
Ehh, we'll let it slide today!
[SEIYA]
But...
[ALL]
(surprised)
But when the chips were down...
I was totally powerless
to carry you guys through it.
[ISUZU]
(gasp)
[SEIYA]
(clears his throat)
But because of all of you...
we came out on the other side.
(voice break)
So... I wanna thank you...
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
(choked up, into cry‐laugh)
[SEIYA] Wha‐?!
[ALL] (laughter)
[SEIYA] Huh?!
[LATIFAH] (giggle)
[MOFFLE] Pfff!
[SEIYA]
B‐be quiet!
Anyway, I have another
big announcement!
Earlier this evening.
We officially closed the deal
to sell off the secondary park
to the south!
The property was purchased
by Moll Mart.
[ALL] (surprised)
[TIRAMY] Wait a minute.
You're talking about that
supermarket chain
that's famous around
the world‐mii!
[SEIYA]
Yep.
It won't be any time soon,
but eventually they're gonna
build
a giant shopping mall
right next to AmaBri.
That should lead to
a nice customer spillover
on both sides.
It'll be perfect synergy!
[ALL]
(amazed)
So when that happens,
you clowns are gonna be so busy
you won't have time to think!
[SEIYA]
(notice)
[WANIPEE]
Oh boy, this is my chance
to really be popular!
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
Something wrong?
[SEIYA]
It's nothing.
(sarcastic applause)
[SEIYA]
What do you want?
[TAKAYA]
Very impressive.
It looks like that prophecy
was right about you after all.
[SEIYA]
(surprised)
How do you know about that?
[TAKAYA]
You tell me, Champ.
[SEIYA]
(angry)
[TAKAYA]
Oops. I guess you can't
read my mind anymore.
You may have gotten lucky
this time, my friend,
but you can't rest on
your laurels forever.
[TAKAYA]
No matter how many visitors
the park may get,
the princess will still be
losing Animus.
In less than half an hour
the date will change over.
And a brand new year
will start from page one.
[SEIYA] (angry)
[TAKAYA]
Glimpsing an ember of hope
only to have it dashed
before your eyes.
[TAKAYA]
I can practically taste
your despair.
And I intend to savor
every morsel!
[SEIYA]
(startled)
[ISUZU]
Kanie!
[MOFFLE]
Moff!
So it was him! All this time!
Moff my words,
I'll crush that bastard!
[SEIYA] What the...?
[ISUZU] He's the one who cast
the curse...
The sorcerer I told you about.
[SEIYA]
(surprised)
[LATIFAH]
It's almost time.
[SEIYA]
Yeah.
[LATIFAH]
I should say...
[ISUZU]
Y‐yes?
Thank you for everything,
Lady Isuzu.
I'm not certain who
I'm going to be
when tomorrow comes but...
I hope you'll support me.
[ISUZU]
Yes... upon my life.
[LATIFAH]
(smile)
And Uncle?
[MOFFLE]
Moff...
Try not to drink so much.
[MOFFLE]
Okay, I'll try.
[LATIFAH]
(sad smile)
Please take care, you three.
[ISUZU]
(kneel)
Lord Moffle...
[LATIFAH]
Sir Kanie.
I don't think I can ever
thank you enough.
[SEIYA]
Uh‐huh...
[LATIFAH]
You seem a little upset.
You think so?
[LATIFAH]
Yes! You haven't even boasted
about your "supreme
intellect" yet.
[LATIFAH]
(troubled)
(starting to cry)
(soft sob)
[LATIFAH]
The truth is...
[SEIYA]
(surprised)
[LATIFAH]
This isn't what I want at all!
Not after I met you... not after
the happy days we all shared!
And not after the wonderful
miracle I witnessed tonight!
[SEIYA]
(stunned)
(sob)I just can't bear...
the fact that I'm
about to forget it all!
[SEIYA]
(choked up)
[LATIFAH]
(crying)
(gasp)
[SEIYA]
It's not much...
but this is all I can do.
[LATIFAH]
(sobbing)
It helps.
[LATIFAH]
(light snooze)
[ISUZU]
That tree...
I don't think it's ever
bloomed that much.
[SEIYA]
I failed her again...
I couldn't...
[LATIFAH]
(stir)
[ISUZU/MOFFLE/SEIYA]
(surprised)
[LATIFAH]
(waking)
Sir Kanie...?
[MOFFLE]
Moff?!
[SEIYA]
You know who I am?!
[LATIFAH]
Well of course I do...
(gasp)
(trembling)
I DO remember!
(extended crying)
[MOFFLE]
(overwhelmed)
Latifah...
[ISUZU]
That tree is called Elpis.
It thrives on Animus for energy.
The amount it consumed
in these three months
was enough to make it bloom.
Animus also alleviates
Her Majesty's curse...
so I can only imagine the
combined happy thoughts
of all the park visitors
were what saved her in the end.
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
Kanie!
[SEIYA]
(surprised)
Sento... What's up?
Are you... leaving now?
Yep! Good riddance!
[ISUZU]
(speechless)
[SEIYA]
(focus, into sigh)
(realize)
(awkward squirming)
Look... Sento...
[ISUZU]
Ah! Wh‐what?
[SEIYA]
Here's the thing...
[ISUZU]
Yes?
(straining)
It's nothing! Bye!
[ISUZU]
(nervous)
[SEIYA]
(annoyed)
(bigger annoyed)
[SEIYA]
Agh, dammit!
[AISU]
(coming in)
Hey, sorry it's so late.
[SEIYA]
How'd things go at work?
[AISU]
Good, we delivered
ahead of schedule.
[SEIYA]
Ohh.
[AISU]
Guess YOU had a rough day.
[SEIYA]
I quit.
You quit?! Already?!
Well, that's a shame.
[SEIYA]
Why's that?
[AISU]
You just looked like
you were having fun.
[SEIYA]
Huh?
Yeah. you seemed excited!
Ever since you first started.
And you've never been
excited about ANYTHING.
Does that surprise you?
(stunned)
[MACARON] (groan)
[TIRAMY] I'm gonna puke‐mii...
[MUSE]
Oh good morning, you two!
[KOBORY]
You don't look well...
[SALAMA]
Are you hungover?
[SYLPHY]
Here comes the miracle dribble
past 11 opponents!
[MACARON]
Ah, youth‐ron...
[TIRAMY]
I'm not doin' squat today...
[SEIYA]
Hey, no lying down on the job!
[ALL] (surprised)
[TIRAMY] Kanie‐mii!
[MACARON] Kanie‐ron!
[MUSE]
I thought you quit yesterday!
[SEIYA]
I changed my mind.
[ALL]
(shock)
Without me, you'll go back
to slacking off all the time...
I'll be keeping an eye
on you from now on.
[MACARON]
Seriously?
[TIRAMY]
He's gone full Big Brother!
[SEIYA]
Quiet! It's almost time to open.
Moff?
We've got work to do,
you lousy rat.
Get busy.
[MOFFLE]
Well, I'll be moffed.
[SEIYA]
Perfect...
Not that I'm surprised.
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
You came back...
[SEIYA]
Sento... Late, I see.
[ISUZU]
Did I miss something?
[SEIYA]
Yeah, this place is a disaster.
If we let our guard down just
because we reached the goal,
it'll ruin everything.
[ISUZU]
You mean... you're...?
Yeah yeah... Enough chit‐chat!
How's the schedule today?
Ah... first we have a
pre‐shift meeting with
all the cast members.
[SEIYA]
Then let's go.
[ISUZU]
(smile)
[LATIFAH]
Sir Kanie!
[SEIYA]
I'm here to stay.
Well, at least until everyone
finally gets their
sorry selves together.
[LATIFAH]
Great!
[SEIYA]
I hope you're grateful!
I'm going out of my way
to bless you with my skills!
Is everything ready to go?!
[ALL]
Yeah!
I want you to give it
all you've got!
[SEIYA]
Open the gates!
Come on in!
[ALL]
Enjoy your day
at Amagi Brilliant Park!
[ISUZU/SEIYA]
Attractions Spotlight!
[SEIYA]
The park is still open!
You wanna do the honors, Sento?
[ISUZU]
Of course.
Today's feature is Space Captain
a thrilling retro sci‐fi
adventure ride.
The hero embarks
on an epic quest
to the far ends of the galaxy.
[SEIYA]
Let me guess, you're about to
tell me something lame that
ruins the whole thing.
[ISUZU]
How did you know?
The ride is currently shut down
because the Captain is suffering
from lower back pain.
[SEIYA]
I knew it.