[SEIYA]
We're having a soccer match!
[ALL]
(confused)
[MOFFLE]
Finally lost your moffin'
marbles, huh?
[SEIYA]
No!
Check this out.
[SEIYA]
You know that stadium
to the south?
We'll hold a soccer match there.
That's our only shot at getting
100,000 people in only ten days.
[ASHE]
You mean we're hosting a
professional match?
[SEIYA]
That's right...
That stadium can hold 50,000.
This is the perfect
chance to use it.
[ISUZU]
As I'm sure some of you have
already surmised,
going by the current rate,
it's impossible to reach half
a million visitors by July 31st.
But if we account
for the projected number
of soccer spectators...
[ALL]
(amazed)
[SEIYA]
Triken!
SIR! As per the acting
manager's orders...
secretly I might add...
...I've been conducting research
for quite some time now.
I followed the few leads I had
all across Japan,
to the north, south,
east, and west.
[TRIKEN]
Oh yes, I went to such great
pains during this whole process
[OKURO] (snore)
that I only wish I could bow
to myself in recogniti‐(pain)
[ISUZU]
Hurry and get to the point.
But Miss Isuzu, I was up all
night preparing‐ (gh!)
[ISUZU] What's that?
[TRIKEN] Yes ma'am!
[SEIYA]
Basically,
I wanted an event that would
make use of the stadium
and bring in more guests...
I was actually on the lookout
for a long time until now.
[MOFFLE]
I had no idea you were
up to something.
I didn't think there was much
chance of finding anything.
[TRIKEN]
However...!
Last night I received a
positive response
from one of my contacts.
[TRIKEN]
This is the home stadium
of Division One team
Grandira Tokyo.
[TRIKEN]
The turf is ragged, so it's
scheduled for refurbishing...
but it's taking them too long
which means that the venue
won't be ready in time
for the commemorative
match on July 31st.
[MOFFLE]
July 31st, huh?
[ISUZU]
That's the date
the team was founded,
so they were hoping to hold
the match on that day.
[ISUZU]
From what we understand,
the annual match between
the current and retired
champion teams
attracts about 50,000.
[SEIYA]
As you might've guessed...
they're in a hurry
to find another venue.
[SEIYA]
So we'll invite them
to come here.
[GENJURO]
But, sir...
I assume we would
need to have some kind of
special license to host a
professional match, wouldn't we?
[ISUZU]
I don't think it's going to be
an official game.
I'm sure it'll work out
if we negotiate properly.
[SEIYA]
We'll tell you more
after we discuss it with them.
[SEIYA]
We're gonna be busy
if it happens.
So you'd better be ready!
[TRIKEN]
Are you sure you'd like ME
to act as AmaBri's main
representative, sir?
[SEIYA]
They won't take us seriously
with a high school
student in charge.
[SEIYA]
Did you bring that
Rarapazzi thing?
[TRIKEN]
Of course. As long as I
have this they won't even
care that I'm a dinosaur.
[SEIYA] (thinking)
[ISUZU] One question.
[SEIYA] Hm?
[ISUZU]
Tell me honestly...
How much of a chance
do you think we have?
[SEIYA]
I don't know.
[GUY A]
It looks like
it's the right size.
[GUY B]
We'll have to see the turf.
[GUY C]
(sigh)
[TRIKEN]
What do you think, sirs?
I'm confident that the capacity
of the stadium
will be enough
to meet your needs.
[GUY C]
From the looks of it,
the building was established
quite a long time ago.
[TRIKEN]
Ah yes...
I‐it's about 20 years old, sir.
[GUY D]
I understand the space
hasn't been used much but...
what kind of regular maintenance
have you been doing?
[TRIKEN]
Um... Well, let me consult
my notes here...
[GUY A]
What about access
from the train station?
How will you manage
50,000 patrons?
[TRIKEN]
(nervous)
I‐I was thinking hard work and
determination would suffice...
[GUY B]
But the most crucial issue
here is the turf...
It has to be all‐natural
and perfectly maintained...
Without that,
there can be no match.
[GUY B]
But I'm sure you know that.
[TRIKEN]
Yes of course I know that...
The turf is very important...
I know.
[ISUZU]
(No he didn't.)
[GUY B]
My concern is that it's
a multipurpose stadium
instead of a sports stadium.
Could you tell us more
about the turf maintenance?
[TRIKEN]
Ah, actually I'm only
Chief of Sales,
so I wouldn't
know the details, sir...
[GUYS]
(sigh)
[GUY C]
Well then, I appreciate
you all taking the time
to come speak with us today.
[ISUZU] (surprised)
[TRIKEN] (shock)
[GUY D]
I think we've heard enough
for now.
We'll get back to you with
a final decision in a few days.
[TRIKEN]
Wait! Please wait a moment!
I urge you to look over our
proposal one more time, please!
It would mean a lot!
[SEIYA]
First off...
you asked us about maintenance?
[GUY A/GUY C]
(surprised)
The park employees are very
dedicated
to keeping the stadium
in excellent condition.
We could do it tomorrow
if you wanted.
[GUY C]
Oh?
[SEIYA]
Then there's accessibility.
We'd be glad to ask a
local bus company to allocate
some shuttle buses.
And our parking lot
has enough space for 5,000 cars.
[GUY D]
(sigh)
[SEIYA]
And we actually have a
specialist on site
who takes care of the turf.
It's immaculately kept
and 100% natural,
so there's no need to worry.
[GUY B]
I'm not so sure.
I invite you to come see
for yourselves...
You won't be disappointed.
[GUY A]
Huh...
[GUY C]
That's all well and good, but...
[GUY D]
We'd rather not work with
a venue with no experience.
[GUY C]
We appreciate your proposal...
(Honestly, the main issue
is how much this'll cost us.)
[GUY D]
(With all the salary
increases, we're struggling
to stay afloat.
We can't afford this.)
[GUY B]
(We couldn't even afford
to finish the turf replacement.
I'm starting to doubt that
we'll be able to pay all
the bills this month.)
[GUY A]
Right... I believe
we have to decline...
(We need to talk the price down
without divulging our
financial problem.)
[SEIYA]
Oh that's right:
I forgot to mention something.
I've discussed this
with my team...
and we've decided
we'd like to waive the fees
and allow you to
use the stadium free of charge.
[GUY A/GUY B/GUY C/GUY D/TRIKEN]
No charge?!
[TRIKEN]
(panicking)
[SEIYA]
That's not all, either...
We recognize bus rentals,
security, advertising,
and ticket printing
can be expensive,
so we're prepared to cover
a portion of those costs as well
if that's alright with you.
[GUY A]
Y‐you're offering
to pay US money?!
[SEIYA]
That's right...
In other words,
Amagi Brilliant Park
is asking to participate
as a sort of sponsor.
[TRIKEN]
A‐are you sure
we can promise that, Mr. Kanie?
[GUY D]
Then we'd be interested
in hearing what kind of numbers
you have in mind specifically.
[SEIYA]
Hm...
[TRIKEN]
(shocked)
[SEIYA]
I think this is reasonable.
[GUY A/GUY B/GUY C/GUY D]
(look)
(amazed)
[SEIYA]
That sound about right?
[GUY A]
W‐wait a minute;
are you sure that isn't some
kind of gross miscalculation?
[SEIYA]
Absolutely positive...
These instructions come directly
from the manager herself.
[GUY B]
It still seems a little high...
[GUY D]
Of course it's extremely
appealing to us, but...
[GUY C]
Aren't you going to
suffer a serious loss?
[SEIYA]
I assure you gentlemen,
our manager is in full support
of the sponsorship
as long as it serves to
bring in some new customers.
She'd like us to host
these soccer fans regardless of
how much it costs the park.
That's exactly what she said.
[GUY A/GUY B/GUY C/GUY D]
(unsure)
[SEIYA]
We do have one
small request, though.
[GUY B/GUY C] (hm?)
[GUY A] And what's that?
[SEIYA]
We'd like all the spectators
to go in through
the park's main gate.
[SEIYA]
Of course, if they have
a soccer ticket,
they'll receive free admission.
[GUY C]
Why would you want to do that?
[GUY D]
It looks like the stadium
has its own separate entrance,
doesn't it?
[SEIYA]
It's too complicated
to explain that...
but I'm afraid this
particular request is
absolutely non‐negotiable.
[GUY C]
Well, I don't see any reason
to take issue with that.
[SEIYA]
(smile)
What do you say, gentlemen?
Why don't you come pay us
a visit soon?
That way you can approve
the facility for yourselves.
[TRIKEN]
Are you sure that was wise?
Promising to pay
the expenses as well?
You must be well
aware of AmaBri's
financial situation, yes?
[SEIYA]
I have a plan.
Trust me.
[ISUZU]
(unsure)
[TRIKEN]
What about the turf maintenance?
I'm not familiar
with any "specialist".
[SEIYA]
What better landscaper
than a flower fairy?
He's got quite the green thumb.
[TIRAMY]
Alright!
Just leave everything to mii!
[TIRAMY] Mii!
[MACARON/MOFFLE] (amazed)
(panic)
[TIRAMY/MOFFLE/MACARON]
Killer plaaant!
[KILLER PLANT]
(hiss)
[TIRAMY]
(startled) (scream)
[MOFFLE/MACARON]
(scream)
[ISUZU]
I was expecting
something like that.
[SEIYA]
Are you guys ready?
Take it down!
[KILLER PLANT]
(dying)
[TARAMO]
Crisis averted, boss!
[ISUZU]
That's wonderful.
[SEIYA]
Yeah.
This oughta do the trick.
[GUY C]
The turf is what really sold us!
I only wish I could convince
you all to tell us your secret.
[GUY D]
Everything's not
exactly perfect...
but we can iron out
the details later on.
[GUY B]
There's not much time
to prepare,
but working together,
I think we'll be able to pull
off this event quite nicely.
[SEIYA]
I appreciate that, sir...
We'll do everything
we can to help out.
[TRIKEN]
We respectfully bow
to you gentlemen.
[GUY B]
Thank you so much...
We look forward to working
with you as well.
[TRIKEN]
(sigh)
That was nerve‐wracking.
[SEIYA]
Sento... tell everybody
to gather on the roof
of Maple Castle
as soon as the
park closes tonight...
I'm breaking the news.
[ISUZU]
I'll do that.
[TRIKEN]
(confused)
What news is that?
[SEIYA]
(troubled)
[ISUZU]
Attention!
[SEIYA]
I have something
I need to tell you.
[SEIYA]
(prepare)
It's important.
[SEIYA]
We're selling off
the south area!
[TIRAMY]
Y‐you say the south area's
gonna be sold‐mii?
[SEIYA]
Right.
It's not up for discussion.
I was looking for a buyer
for a while...
[SEIYA]
...and the other day
I finally found one.
The money we make
from that should take care
of our financial issue...
I'm sure you all understand.
[WRENCH]
Heh, there ya go
droppin' another bomb on us.
[MUSE]
But Mr. Kanie, the southern
area's almost as big
as the main section!
[MUSE]
You can't‐
[SEIYA]
I can and I will.
[WANIPEE]
I always thought AmaBri would
get back on its feet one day
and maybe we could build
some nice attractions
over in that area.
[NICK]
Me too, I figured
that was the plan.
[DORNELL]
Yeah, if we could've expanded,
it would've really put AmaBri
on the map once and for all.
[SEIYA]
None of that stuff
is ever gonna happen!
Not before this park
runs itself into the ground!
If we have to cut off
a limb to survive, then
that's exactly what we'll do!
We can't afford to think about
what happens after this.
[MOFFLE] Okay.
[MUSE/SYLPHY] Huh?
Maybe it's not such a
bad idea‐ y'know?
[MUSE]
Mr. Moffle...
That's true, maybe hanging
onto land we're not using
is kind of a waste‐ron.
[TIRAMY]
Fair enough...
Guess I'm on board‐mii.
[ASHE]
It does make sense
from an accounting
perspective as well...
It's better if we can solve
everything at once.
[MUSE]
Maybe you're right...
I just think it'll be sad
to give up half of the property.
[KOBORY]
I know, but it's for
the good of the park.
[SALAMA]
Sounds like the best way for
us to keep working together...
so I can't really complain.
[SYLPHY]
You can't make an omelet
without breaking eggs!
[WRENCH] I reckon I'll allow it.
[GENJURO] Right! Lose the
battle, win the war!
[SEIYA]
(focus) Good!
That's all I needed to tell you.
[SEIYA]
We've got 9 days left,
and there's still a lot to do!
[SEIYA]
Starting tonight, nobody's
going home or taking days off!
Now get to work, everyone!
YEAH!
[LATIFAH]
How are the preparations going?
[SEIYA]
Well, I can't say it's
a walk in the park,
but I think we can manage it.
[LATIFAH]
That's wonderful to hear,
Sir Kanie.
[SEIYA] I'm uh... sorry.
[LATIFAH] About what?
About my decision to sell almost
half of the park property.
I know I discussed it
with you first...
but I'm sorry it had to happen.
[LATIFAH]
How many times must I say it?
You are the manager
of our precious park, Sir Kanie.
[LATIFAH]
We trust you to serve
its best interest.
[SEIYA]
(speechless)
[LATIFAH]
More importantly, isn't there
something I can do to help?
I feel terrible sitting here
doing nothing while you're
all working so diligently.
[SEIYA]
For now, your job
is to get some rest...
Don't worry about anything else.
[LATIFAH] I don't know...
What? Now you can't follow
the acting manager's orders?
[LATIFAH]
(laugh) Very well then.
[SEIYA]
Just sit back and relax.
I mean... think about how
much better
this place is doing
lately all because of me.
And once we get to August,
it'll be even bet‐ (realize)
[LATIFAH]
(troubled)
[SEIYA]
Oh wait...
the first of August...
That's when you're gonna lose
all your memories again, right?
[SEIYA]
Even if the park stays open.
[LATIFAH]
Please don't let it trouble you.
It's just something
that happens every year.
I can't believe you've been
living your life this way
for such a long time now.
[LATIFAH]
Yes...
At the stroke of midnight
on the first day of August...
my physical body as well as my
memories are set back by a year.
[LATIFAH]
My uncle explained
the situation to me
when it happened the last time.
[LATIFAH]
The reason I'm here...
and what's happened
up until now.
I'm sure I must have met
the Digerry Clan and Sir Rubrum
at some point as well...
but I don't have
any memory of that.
[SEIYA]
Oh.
But I know that as long as
this park exists,
I'll always be here.
[LATIFAH]
Always and forever.
[SEIYA]
(sad)
[LATIFAH]
So please...
Come back and visit me
whenever you can,
even after
you finish working here.
For some odd reason I never
forget how to make croquettes.
[SEIYA]
Okay...
I do like your croquettes.
[LATIFAH]
Right! We can ride
the Ferris wheel again too!
[SEIYA]
Ah! Uh, maybe not that.
[LATIFAH]
Oh, I forgot!
I'm sorry. (giggles)
[TAKAYA]
Hey there, it's been a while.
You know, you're always
barging in.
[TAKAYA]
I just came to check
the old visitor counter.
Not giving up, are you?
[SEIYA]
Yeah, I think we'll
just barely make 500,000.
[TAKAYA]
Just to make this clear...
the contract deadline is at
closing time on the last day,
which is 9 o'clock sharp.
No extensions allowed...
Please remember that.
[SEIYA]
Well the soccer match
kicks off at 6PM...
So there's nothing
to worry about.
[TAKAYA]
I'll send one of my staff
the day‐of.
[TAKAYA]
July 31st at 9 p. m.
I'll be looking forward to it.
[SEIYA]
(look)
[ISUZU]
Kanie... It's time to go.
[SEIYA]
Right.
Unlock the gate!
We're open!
[MOFFLE]
(juggling)
[MOTHER A]
Oh my, they're lovely!
[LITTLE GIRL]
How did he do that?
[MACARON]
Ro‐Ron!
[FUTURE]
Keep our planet clean!
[GIRL]
Look at me so I can take your
picture with the ferret guy!
[MUSE]
Hey guys!
Ready?
[SALAMA]
That's awesome!
[KOBORY]
We sure hope all of you
enjoy the show today!
[ISUZU]
The numbers really
are climbing up.
[SEIYA]
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
we'll get even more.
We HAVE to get more.
[TRIKEN]
Current wait time is 20 minutes!
I repeat, the current
wait time is 20 minutes!
[TIRAMY]
Miii!!!
[GIRL B]
Aw, he's so cute!
[TIRAMY]
Mii! Mii! Mii‐heehee!
(sigh) Jeez,
when's it gonna be over...
[GIRL C]
Look Mom! It's Tiramy!
[TIRAMY]
(startled) Another one?!
ENCORE ENCORE!
[MACARON]
How many encores
do they want from me‐ron?
[MOFFLE]
Moff! All units follow me!
(panic) (dizzy falling) (oof!)
[GENJURO]
Hyahhhh!
[EIKO]
I'm sorry, we're full!
but please feel free
to wait for the next showtime!
I need two carbonaras,
an order of hotcakes,
three udon bowls,
and what was that other thing...
two bowls of ramen!
[SHIINA]
W‐w‐wait a minute‐ there's no
way I can remember all thaaat!
[NICK]
Hey Shiina! We're running low
on meat again!
Go pick some up from
that store near the station!
[SHIINA]
Not again!
Get as much as you can carry!
We're gonna need at least
200 pounds of it this time!
[BIINO/SHIINA]
(panic)
[LITTLE BOY A]
(loud crying)
[WANIPEE]
We don't have
enough personnel!
Send some backup to
the Lost Child Center ASAP!
[MACARON]
Ugh, I'm so exhausted.
[KOBORY]
I've never even seen this many
people at comic conventions.
[SALAMA]
This has gotta be
some kind of park record.
[TIRAMY]
I can't feel my feet, mii.
Sure wish a nice girl
would give me a massage.
[MUSE]
Sorry! that's
never gonna happen.
[MOFFLE]
It's only gonna get busier
in the afternoon.
[MOFFLE]
We'll just have to stick it out.
[PA VOICE]
It's time for
the special event...
All cast members
please be on standby.
[MACARON]
Already?!
[KOBORY/MUSE/SALAMA]
(weary)
[BOY A]
Come on Dad!
It's almost time!
[DAD]
Slow down buddy,
we'll get there.
[MUSE]
(smile)
[MOFFLE]
Someday we'll be this crowded
without the help
of some soccer match.
[MUSE]
Yeah.
[GUY E] It's over there!
[GUY F] Sweet, let's go!
[ISUZU]
The people who came in
on the last bus
just went through the gate.
[SEIYA]
(gasp, into shock)
[ISUZU]
(startled) Kanie!
[SEIYA]
(look)
We fell short.
[ISUZU/SEIYA]
Time for the
attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU]
Today's feature is
Fisherman's Dive.
[SEIYA]
Is this really necessary?
The park might
be about to shut down.
[ISUZU]
That's exactly
why it's important.
[SEIYA]
Fine.
So, what's Fisherman's Dive?
[ISUZU]
A coaster ride in Splash Ocean,
based on Hemingway's
famous masterpiece.
[ISUZU]
Visitors struggle desperately
to catch an impressive marlin
only to be thwarted by sharks.
[SEIYA]
That's not fun!