Darn, that cute office girl
isn't here today.
Oh, no, I hope this skirt
isn't too short.
Yoritomo, 1185...
No!
[ISUZU] What happened?
It's 1192!
He's got his years mixed up!
[ISUZU] Just leave him alone.
[SEIYA] (grrr)
[ISUZU] Can I assume you
believe what I've told you now?
A kiss from a member of the
Maple Land royal family
has the ability to
grant magic powers.
[SEIYA]
Did you say "royal family"?
[ISUZU] Yes, she's a princess.
It would appear that you've
been given the power
to perceive what the people
around you are thinking.
Try it on me.
There was one other person
who possessed this power
in the past,
but it could never work
more than once on
the same individual.
Wait, you mean if I tried to
read your mind again later...
It wouldn't work.
You tricked me into
doing it this time
so that I'll never know
what you're thinking.
That might be the reason.
But why would you guys want
to give me some superpower
like this?
So you'd be more inclined to
take the manager position.
[SEIYA] (grrrr)
[ISUZU] We'll be returning to
the park after school.
No way‐ (urk!)
[door opens] (ah!)
[LATIFAH] Uncle! (giggles)
[MOFFLE]
I'm sorry I couldn't stop by and
visit you yesterday, Latifah.
Oh, no, that's all right.
Did you get acquainted with
that Kanie kid?
Yes, but he fell unconscious
during the magic‐granting
ritual.
So, I asked Lady Isuzu to
watch over him after that.
Moff, that means he
and Latifah must've...
What?
Don't worry about it.
I just hope he's not
inappropriate with Isuzu.
What do you mean by
"inappropriate"?
Moff! Uh, well, you'll
understand when you're older...
[gasp] Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot.
(sigh)
I know it might not
happen this year,
but I'll keep on wishing for it.
I believe that,
with Sir Kanie's help,
things might just
turn around for us.
Moff...
Macaron! (laughing)
Tiramy! (laughing)
[MACARON] Ron!
[TIRAMY] Mii!
Aw, isn't that sweet? You've
got them all to yourselves.
That was fun!
I wanna stay, Mom!
[MACARON] Ron! Ron!
[TIRAMY] Mii!
[MACARON & TIRAMY] (uhhhhhh...)
I swear, I was this close to
murdalizing those little brats!
Try to relax.
You'll never make it
in this business
if you get upset every time
the kids beat you up.
But they kept punching the
crap out of me like THIS!
[MACARON] (ow, ow, ow)
And then they were
hitting me like THAT!
[MACARON] (ow, ow, ow)
[fight bell rings]
[MACARON] HIT ME AGAIN, PUNK!
[TIRAMY] First, they
came at me like THAT and THAT,
and then they were‐
[MOFFLE] It's too moffin'
early for this.
[MACARON] Oh, hey, it's Moffle!
[TIRAMY] Good morning, mii!
You look even more
cranky than usual.
[MOFFLE]
Yeah, it's about the kid.
Oh, you mean the one Isuzu was
giving the grand tour?
So, what did you think of him?
[MOFFLE] He's a narcissist
with a bad attitude.
Just thinking about him
pisses me off.
[MUSE]
Well, good morning, everybody!
[MOFFLE] (huh?)
[TIRAMY] (ah!) Oh, wow, you look
cute as always, Muse!
[giggles]
[TIRAMY] And Kobory,
you're as elegant as usual.
Thank you.
[TIRAMY] Salama,
you're as callous as ever.
And of course Sylphy's not
listening at all!
[SYLPHY] (laughing)
I'm a helicopter!
Are You girls off
to Elementario?
[SYLPHY] (helicopter noises)
Yes, it's time for the
first show of the day.
[MOFFLE] If that little
ingrate takes over,
[SALAMA] Who cares,
we don't stand a chance.
[SALAMA] nobody's gonna show up.
[SEIYA]
I still have a ton of questions.
I mean, what kind of place is
this Maple Land anyway?
It's a magical kingdom resting
on the edge of land and water,
and Latifah happens
to be its princess.
Actually, there was another
thing she said before
I passed out
that struck me as weird.
I think she was talking about
losing the power to live
or something?
That would be Animus.
Animus?
[ISUZU]
It's the crystallized happiness
of all the guests
who visit the park.
Basically,
Animus is our life energy.
[SEIYA] Huh?
AmaBri is a facility used to
gather the Animus we need.
All of the establishments that
exist for that purpose are what
we call Argels.
Are you trying to tell me that
whether or not they decide to
close that old rundown park
is a life‐or‐death situation
for you people?
Yes, of course.
[ISUZU] Several other theme
parks are secretly
Argels as well.
You mean Maple Land built all
those other big parks
in the area too?
Oh, no, there are multiple
magical worlds,
so each one of them establishes
an Argel for themselves.
Magical realms are powerless
without a supply of Animus.
That's why the parks are
so desperate to get guests.
And what happens if the
kingdom runs out of Animus?
[sad sigh]
Then we cease to exist.
How are you doing this morning,
Miss Isuzu?
[ISUZU] Hello.
[SEIYA] Is that guy from
the magical land?
No, actually Okuro's an
ordinary human being.
There are several other
non‐magical residents
working at AmaBri as well.
[SEIYA] What's this?
[ISUZU] Staff housing.
I also live in there.
But the place I wanted you to
visit today is the
administrative building.
[ISUZU] Here we are.
Moff...
[grrr]
Are you going to fight?
No getting around it.
[air raid siren]
Moff moff moff moff!
[SEIYA] Bring it on! (urk!)
Are you two done bonding now?
You really think
this is bonding?!
We should go.
We'll be late
if we don't hurry up.
Great, NOW what are you
gonna put me through?
I want to introduce you
to the enemy.
Huh?
My name is Takaya Kurisu.
I'm here from Amagi Development.
Uh, thank you.
I don't think we've met before.
That's Seiya Kanie;
he's an intern.
Shouldn't the manager
be here as well?
She wasn't feeling
very well today.
Since I'm the acting manager,
I'll be the one to consider
your proposal.
[SEIYA] (huh?)
[TAKAYA]
I see; that's all right then.
[TAKAYA] I'm sure you
already know this,
but your contract stipulates
that the annual visitor count
must be calculated beginning on
August 1st of every year,
and that if you fall short of
half a million guests for
five years in a row,
Amagi Development receives
full control of the park.
[ISUZU] Yes.
[TAKAYA] The park has
fallen below 500,000 attendees
[SEIYA] (hmm?)
for four consecutive years now.
You're at 250,000 for the year.
And it's already May.
I'm afraid you have less than
three months remaining.
And you see,
from where I'm standing,
you haven't even begun
preparations to shut down.
That's correct.
Because we can't be certain
that the visitor count
won't surpass 500,000 before
the deadline is up.
(big sigh)
Tell me you're not serious.
Summer break is
just around the corner!
I'm sure we'll get‐
[TAKAYA] Summer break
starts in late July.
Two weeks won't be enough
to save your park.
You're generating a
considerable deficit.
If I were you, I'd start
getting my assets in order.
Allow me to give you
a little example here.
Let's say a family of four
takes a vacation to
Amagi Brilliant Park.
Would you make a profit based on
last year's attendance?
Well, it depends on how much the
family needs to spend every day,
which is...
85,000 yen.
That's almost on the nose.
It's actually 83,200.
[TAKAYA]
That was quite impressive.
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[TAKAYA] How would you like
to come work with us?
[ISUZU] (ah!)
Nah, don't think I'm interested.
Well that's a shame.
In any case, those are the
numbers we're looking at here.
You just can't keep up this
indulgence of yours
for much longer.
But, sir, if you give us a
chance, then maybe we could...
A chance, huh?
Face it, the only thing
you can do now
is pray that another quarter
million people are stupid enough
to waste their time
at this dump.
[ISUZU] (grrr)
[TAKAYA] No offense.
You didn't tell me you were
the acting manager.
[ISUZU]
Princess Latifah needed me to do
it for a year to take her place.
[ISUZU] Did you come up with
the 85,000 yen
because you were reading
Mr. Kurisu's mind earlier?
No, all I did was
make a rough estimate
based on the size of the park
and yesterday's visitor count.
It's a little math trick
called a Fermi estimate.
[ISUZU] I don't understand.
Look it up sometime.
More importantly,
why did you bring me here
to meet with those people?
[umm...]
If you're going to be
the manager of AmaBri,
you'll need to know
who we're up against.
Would you just drop it?
[sigh]
You take away my free time after
school and on the weekends,
you repeatedly threaten me with
that ridiculous gun of yours,
and yet you STILL expect me to
help you save this stupid
theme park?
Who in their right mind would
say yes after all that?
I'm sorry, I'm not quite
accustomed to this world yet.
I don't know the appropriate way
to ask for someone's help.
So you shoot them?
[ISUZU] Yes.
[waaah!]
[ISUZU]
Steinberger is a magical weapon
compatible with several
types of bullets.
[SEIYA] Put that away!
The bullet I shot you with
before was called a
Pain Bringer.
That variety is enough to cause
double the amount of pain of
stubbing your pinky toe.
[SEIYA] Put it down!
I don't see why you would ask me
instead of somebody with
professional management
experience.
We tried that,
but then they all quit on us.
[SEIYA] Why?
Perhaps they
didn't like being shot at.
[SEIYA] Really?!
I feel like this is
all my fault.
That's why I came
to your school.
I was so desperate,
I needed you to agree to help
no matter what the cost!
[sigh]
I've had enough.
You're leaving?!
[SEIYA] Yep.
But you can't! You're the only
chance we've got, Kanie!
Please save our park!
I can't help you.
But what about the Princess?!
Hey, there.
Hey.
[hmm?]
What now?
You're Seiya Kodama,
the child actor!
[SEIYA] You're mistaken.
No, no, I'm sure.
ut why's a big
celebrity like you
working part‐time in
a rundown amusement park?
I said‐
[grumpy sigh]
It's none of your business.
[TAKAYA] Well, I'm sure
you've got your reasons,
but here's some advice:
Don't be stupid, all right?
If you spend your time
around losers,
you'll end up a loser yourself.
[grrr]
Take care.
[car door shuts]
I guess the corners are round
so kids don't get hurt.
How can they have time for
little details like that
when the place is such a wreck?
Jeez, get your
priorities in order.
Either way, I should get them to
do something about these crazy
psychic powers.
[panting]
[lots of people talking]
I hope they're not gonna give
us some kind of bad news.
I'm surprised you haven't
already heard something,
Mr. Moffle.
What's your take on it,
Mr. Cast Leader?
[SYLPHY] Un, deux, trois!
Moff, I bet it's exactly
what you think it is.
[SYLPHY] Un, deux, trois!
[ISUZU]
Everyone, your attention please!
[SYLPHY] Wheee!
[ISUZU] The first princess
of Maple Land, Her Royal
Highness Latifah Fullanza
would like to address
her subjects!
This is an important message!
[CAST GUY] All right,
let's get this over with.
[concerned murmurs]
[CAST GIRL] I had a feeling
this was coming.
These people sure do
give up easily.
Can't really blame 'em.
Good evening, my friends.
It is with a heavy heart
that I must impart some
very upsetting news today.
In three months' time,
our Amagi Brilliant Park will
be permanently shut down.
[shoked gasps & confusion]
[LATIFAH]
I know it hurts to say goodbye,
but I promise I'll do everything
I can to find new jobs for
every one of you.
And even though the road ahead
is certain to introduce
some challenges‐
[WANIPEE] Challenges, really?!
[LATIFAH & ISUZU] (gasps)
But, Your Majesty, hardly
anybody out there even
knows who I am!
It's too late for me to
build up a fan base now!
What am I gonna do?!
Well I...
I'm not quite sure,
but if you try hard then‐
[WANIPEE]
What's the use of trying?!
I'll just wind up
passing out tissues
in front of some
train station anyway!
And then before you know it,
everybody'll forget about me
forever! (hysterical sobbing)
[concerned gasps]
[WANIPEE] Without fans,
I'll just disappear!
[LATIFAH] (sigh)
How could you let us down
like this, Princess?! (sobbing)
[MOFFLE]
Put a sock in it, Wanipee.
But I'm sad!
How many years have you
worked at AmaBri?
[WANIPEE] About twelve.
Then you've had more
than enough chances.
It's your own fault you
relied too much on the park
and didn't establish
your own fan base.
[WANIPEE] (gasp)
[MOFFLE]
So why are you making a scene?
Because... becaaaaause!
(sobbing)
[MOFFLE] Don't worry, Wanipee.
I'll be right there passing
out tissues with you, okay?
If you work hard,
you still have a chance
of being successful
as a local mascot
or something like that.
[WANIPEE] Easy for you to say.
Moff?
Come on, Moffle, we both know
you could easily move on
to some other theme park.
Why would I do a
fool thing like that?
You're practically identical to
Macky at Urayasu Digimarland!
Did you really think
nobody noticed?!
[MOFFLE] Moff...
[WANIPEE] He's a mouse too,
I'm sure you could get a good
gig as a sidekick‐(choking)
[MOFFLE]
I'm nobody's sidekick! Got it?!
I've built my career on
originality!
I'm not a knockoff or a
sidekick, buster!
[WANIPEE] (crying)
That hurts! Let me go!
Both of you, cut it out!
[BOTH] (huh?)
[MACARON] We're in front
of the princess, ron!
[MOFFLE] (concerned)
[MACARON] She's suffering more
than anybody right now.
Can't you two see that?
[WANIPEE] (oofff)
Sorry I got upset.
No...
This is all my fault.
I've failed.
I'm so sorry!
If only I'd been able
to save this place...
I know it's not enough, but...
I truly do apologize.
And I hope...
I hope you'll all forgive me...
if you can.
Don't you think it's a little
early for you to apologize?
[BOTH] (gasp!)
[ALL] (huh?)
[deep breath]
You really are
a hopeless bunch.
If you're gonna feel sorry
for yourselves,
at least wait until
you've actually lost.
Is he the one the prophesy
told us about?
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
Huh?
What are you doing
back here, punk?
If I remember correctly,
you clowns forced me to
come here against my will.
[MOFFLE] They told me you turned
down the manager position.
Just get lost already!
I don't think so.
I'm actually in the mood
to help you losers with
your little problem now.
[BOTH] (gasp!)
We can handle it
just fine on our own!
We don't need help
from the likes of you!
Heh! Yeah, you LOOK like
you're handling it.
Moffu?
Come on!
Every one of you is useless!
You can't attract business
or make money,
and now you're all about
to lose your jobs!
Oh, and guess what that guy
from Amagi Development
said to me earlier.
That you'd have to be a moron
to spend your money at
this trash heap!
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
[ALL] (grrr)
He's right! The poor,
misguided saps who DO come
are wasting their hard‐earned
cash on a pitiful excuse
for an amusement park
that's not even bad enough
to be so‐bad‐it's‐good!
Seriously, even I don't know
what to say to that!
And what have you idiots
been doing in the meantime?
Nothing! You're just whining
and complaining!
It's true!
I'd feel pretty stupid
if I gave my money to a
pathetic lot like you!
All right,
now I'm really getting mad!
[LATIFAH] Please stand down.
[MOFFLE] Huh?
[LATIFAH]
I do apologize, Sir Kanie.
Would you please come
and join us on the balcony?
Heh...
[SEIYA]
I should introduce myself.
Name's Seiya Kanie.
And I don't even have
to read your minds
to know what you're
all thinking.
Let me see here, uh...
Aha! That's right, you hate
my guts already, don't you?
"Where'd this jerk come from?"
"How can we entrust HIM
with our precious park?"
"What could he possibly do
in three months?"
And that's not all!
"Princess Latifah with
a jackass like him?"
[LATIFAH (ah!)
[SEIYA] "I can't bear
to think about it!"
Have I pissed you off enough?
Good!
From now on,
it's not in your hands anymore.
I'm your new dictator!
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
If you don't like that,
I'll fire you right now!
You will do exactly
as I tell you to do!
This lousy park is gonna
close down either way,
so I might as well
do what I want!
That said, I guarantee you'll
be amazed in the end.
In these three months,
this random kid you hate
is gonna pull off a miracle
like you've never seen!
[CAST] (wow!)
I'll get you those
250,000 customers.
And that prophesy
or whatever?
I WILL make it come true!
[ISUZU] A stunt?
[SEIYA] Yeah,
I made them angry on purpose.
[LATIFAH] Why would you do that?
Well, when I told them your
customers were all morons,
that made the cast
get really mad.
The fact that they were that
offended by me talking smack
about the customers
means they're serious.
So, there's still hope.
Oh, I never thought of that.
You mean, you've decided to
help us out after all?
[SEIYA] Yeah.
[ISUZU & LATIFAH]
(relieved sigh)
Three months, no more, no less.
After that, I'm washing
my hands of all of this.
Right.
You have my deepest gratitude.
[sigh]
Don't go thanking me just yet.
[LATIFAH] (huh?)
Well, I'm gonna give it
my best shot, but...
Just don't get your hopes up.
It's virtually impossible.
But what about your
big speech earlier?!
[SEIYA] I said what I had to.
[ISUZU] (ah!)
[LATIFAH] (hmm...)
[SEIYA]
If we want to succeed here,
we need them to have
a little hope left.
Well, in that case,
I won't give up either.
Because your prophesy tells you
I'm gonna make this happen?
[LATIFAH]
No. The Oracle does give us a
little guidance for our lives,
but I have no idea what the
future truly holds for us.
Then what's your reason?
Because you agreed to help us
save the park, Sir Kanie.
I know things are
going to change.
And I believe that AmaBri
has a chance to make
a brighter future.
[resigned sigh]
[ISUZU] These are the
documents you asked for.
[SEIYA] Thanks.
[ISUZU] Is there anything else?
[SEIYA] No.
[ISUZU]
Did you let your family know you
wouldn't be going home tonight?
[SEIYA] Yeah.
[ISUZU] I'll leave a blanket for
you so you can get some sleep.
[SEIYA] 'Kay.
And Kanie?
[SEIYA] (hmmm?)
Thanks for this.
Sure.
Hey! Good to see
you again, Mr. Moffle!
Chilled tomatoes and a beer.
'Kay!
[MACARON] Yo buddy, ron!
Started without ya.
[TIRAMY] Mii, what took ya?
[MOFFLE] Moff!
Sorry to keep you waiting, sir.
I brought you a beer!
[MOFFLE] Moff.
Hey, baby, ron, could you bring
us two more of those, please?
[TAKAMI] Uh‐huh.
[TIRAMY] And hurry back
with that sweet ass, mii!
[TAKAMI] Oh, you!
You really ought to watch your
language when you go out
in public, Tiramy.
You never know who might be
listening to what you say.
[TIRAMY] Relax, that's what
these Rarapazzi charms are for.
As long as we're
wearing these babies,
nobody'll find out
we're fairies!
Those only change your
appearance, you knucklehead.
We'd be in hot water if word
got out that an AmaBri mascot
was drinking beer and
checking out women's butts!
[TIRAMY] (grrr)
Mii! Stop tellin' me
how to live my life!
What's the fun of goin' out
drinkin' if you can't check out
the tits and ass?!
[MACARON] You better zip
that dirty mouth!
[TIRAMY] (choking)
Stop acting so stupid!
[ALL] We're sorry.
And cheers!
What's gotcha down today,
Moff‐man?
[MACARON] (chugging) (ah!)
Is it that Kanie kid again?
[MOFFLE] Moff!
Well, we might as well stick
it out till the end, right?
I'm kinda curious to see what
his game plan is, honestly.
[grrr]
[confusion murmurs]
[MOFFLE] What the hell does that
rat bastard think he's doing?!
[ISUZU & SEIYA] Time for
the attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU] Today's feature is
Macaron's Music Theatre.
[SEIYA]
I haven't been in there yet.
What's it like?
[ISUZU] A sanctuary of sound
filled to the brim
with the most
prestigious of legends.
[SEIYA] Wow, that sounds
pretty sophisticated.
What kind of legends?
[ISUZU] Like when Macaron got
into a fist‐fight with some
rude audience members
and the whole stage collapsed.
[SEIYA] That's prestigious?!