[sigh]
I look great in anything.
Seiya Kanieeee!
[SEIYA] (huh?) (urk!)
[MOFFLE]
You have to stop this now!
[SEIYA] (blocking effort)
Stop what?!
[MOFFLE] Closing for the day!
And what makes you think
I'm taking orders from you?!
In all twenty‐nine years
of operation,
this park has never once been
closed without notice!
The public's come to
trust us for that.
But now... you...
You're gonna pay for this!
[SEIYA] Hyaaah!
Wait, I see a pattern!
You scumbag...
Now it's YOUR turn to pay!
[gun fires]
[BOTH] (uhun...)
[ISUZU] No fighting.
[SEIYA] How did you fire twice
from a muzzleloader?
Try to calm down, Lord Moffle.
[MOFFLE] How can you
tell me to calm down?
Thanks to him, we're
gonna have to disappoint
all the attendees
who show up today!
I refuse to let this guy
disrespect our park!
[SEIYA]
We have to clean up the place.
That's the first step.
Shut your mouth! What does
a wise guy like you know
about a park he's only been at
for the last two days?!
[ISUZU] (sigh)
[SEIYA] (huh?)
[SEIYA] (hmm...)
I hate to admit it,
but you bring up a good point.
Maybe you'd better go take care
of the guests then.
[MOFFLE] Moff?!
[SEIYA]
I don't care how you do it.
Just go entertain the guests in
the square outside the main
entrance.
Huh? But what am I gonna do
in that big empty space?
What? You can't do it?
Uh! O‐Of course I can!
[hmpf!]
[MOFFLE] Watch and learn!
[SEIYA] This building is
kept up pretty well.
It looks like the little rat
DOES take his job seriously
after all.
Don't you still have a lot of
attractions you wanted us to
inspect today, Kanie?
[SEIYA] I know.
I see you all made it.
[SEIYA] Let's get this
administration meeting started.
Keeping it short,
we've got three goals.
[SEIYA] Number one!
I want the park
to stay open later!
[ALL] Boo...
[SEIYA] Stop complaining
like a bunch of kids!
Well, I figure that all depends
on how much later we're
talkin' about here.
We ain't got the facilities
to keep this place runnin'
after dark,
so I reckon after sundown
it'll be a no‐go.
I already thought of that.
First, we'll extend the park
hours to 7pm instead of 5.
In the meantime,
we can start setting up
whatever facilities we need so
that we can operate at night.
And THEN we'll stretch it to 9pm
when we're ready.
How's that?
Well, I guess that doesn't
sound too bad.
Second! There's no more
regular days off!
[ALL] Boo...
[SEIYA] Jeez, you people
are such babies!
I mean, seriously, how do you
expect your business to succeed
if you're closed on FRIDAYS?!
You never heard of TGIF?
[NICK] (chuckle)
Forget it! That's the
best possible time to
rake in the cash!
Listen! From tomorrow morning
until July 31st,
not one of you is getting
a single day off!
You understand?!
[ALL] Fine.
I guess we should have
seen that coming.
Third! And this is the big one.
I've decided that from now
until the end of July,
access to the park and
all attractions will be
totally free of charge!
[ALL] HUH?!
[ISUZU] (huh?)
[MOFFLE] You're kidding me!
[SEIYA] Nope.
With all due respect,
as Chief of Accounting,
I must disagree.
With AmaBri consistently
in the red,
there's no way we can afford
to do something like that.
[WRENCH] Can't pay the bills
on free admission, boss man.
[hmpf]
[MOFFLE] Besides, we're pros.
You can't expect us to entertain
without some kind of paycheck.
[SEIYA] Ha, you call punching
people entertainment?
Argh! I apologize for
what I did, all right?
But regardless of what
we're doing, we can't do it
for nothing.
If we make everything free,
even temporarily,
we'll never get people to
pay money for it again.
That'll be the end of
AmaBri for sure.
Hmm... Well, I knew you guys
wouldn't be too happy
with the changes.
And your concerns here
are pretty valid.
Let me think...
Okay, instead of nothing, we'll
charge 30 yen for everything.
[ALL] HUH?!
[MOFFLE] Why 30 of all things?
[SEIYA]
Because I hear this park's
about to hit its 30th
anniversary next year.
I'm sorry, but charging them
30 yen for everything
is essentially the same concept
as charging nothing at all.
Look, we need visitors
more than cash right now.
If we screw up, there won't BE
a park to pay bills on.
Now unless you have
more questions,
I'll adjourn the meeting so you
can get back to your posts.
Carry on!
[deep sigh]
[MOFFLE]
30 yen is pocket change!
You said that already.
Moffin' hardass!
That basically tells us our
skills are worth nothing to him!
I won't stand for this!
There's no point in
getting angry, ron.
Come on, Macaron,
aren't you mad at all?
Think about it this way,
Moffle‐ron,
if we don't get visitors in the
door, we'll be done for,
so we gotta do whatever we can
do to survive for a while.
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
You ready to rock the house,
Mr. Sweets Fairy‐ron?
I wouldn't have it any
other way, Mr. Music Fairy.
(chuckle)
Okay, let's put this
behind us for a minute
and give those kids
a moffin' good show!
[MOFFLE] Moff!
[MACARON] Ron!
You're stupiiiiiiid!
[MOFFLE] (oof!)
[ALL] (huh?)
[TAKESHI]
I wanted to go to Digimarland,
and then we come here and
you're not even OPEN?!
Say you're sorry, ya knockoff!
[MOFFLE] (grrr!)
I'm really sorry, little guy.
Stop kicking that thing,
Takeshi!
(huh?)
[MOFFLE] Must be his mom.
Good thing she stopped him
or I might've killed him.
A lot of people put their grubby
hands on these costumes, dear.
Don't touch it or you might get
a disease! Do you understand me?
Yes, ma'am.
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
If anything happens
to my little boy,
your park will be hearing
from my lawyer.
You'd better watch yourself,
knockoff!
[SALAMA] Hashtag brutal!
[MUSE] (uh‐oh)
Please don't start
another flame war.
[MOFFLE]
Oh, so you were just worried
about your precious hellspawn.
But...
[TAKESHI'S MOM] (gasp)
You picked the wrong mouse!
[TAKESHI'S MOM] (ah!)
I don't think so, mister. I'll
make you regret toying with me!
Wait, did you just talk?
[TAKESHI] (huh?!)
Uh‐oh, ron.
[TAKESHI] Daddy, Daddy!
[TAKESHI'S DAD]
Yeah, little man?
Would you believe this
disgusting park employee
just assaulted me?
[TAKESHI'S DAD Oh, yeah?
Didn't your boss ever tell ya
the customer's always right?
Lose the stupid costume and I'll
teach you a lesson, ya knockoff!
[MOFFLE]
Every customer is a god.
Huh?
[MOFFLE] But still,
whether you're a god or not...
[TAKESHI'S DAD]
Speak up, I can't hear ya.
There's certain things
that shouldn't be said!
What's that look for?
Do ya want me to give ya an
ass‐kickin'? Is that it?
All right...
Then say your prayers!
Don't do iiiiit!
[TAKESHI'S DAD] (hyung!)
(ooff!) (ungh)
[BOTH] (gasp!) (waahhh...)
Crap! I was too late, ron!
Hey, Mommy, there's something
funny about that mascot.
Shush! What did I tell you
about these things?
[MOFFLE] You just take
a little nap, okay?
[BOTH] (waahhh!)
Now it's your turn
to learn something.
Get ready to find out
what happens to mouthy
humans like you
who dare to accuse me
of being a knockoff!
[BOTH] (waaahhh!)
Thanks for visiting
Amagi Brilliant Park!
[BOTH] (WAAAHHH!!)
[MOFFLE] (oof!)
[SEIYA] I don't think so!
[gun fires]
[BOTH] (gasps!)
[BOTH] (waahhh...)
Forgotten Realm Bullets,
they're memory erasers.
[SEIYA] (aaahhh...)
I'm sure they'll wake up soon.
[SEIYA] Oh God,
I just witnessed a crime...
Ah, you get used to
it eventually.
[SEIYA] Yeah, I doubt that!
More importantly,
why in the hell did you have to
use violence on customers
in the first place?!
If the public finds out,
we'll be screwed!
What were you thinking?!
I know it was a dumb
thing to do, all right?
[SEIYA]
Please don't tell me this is
like an everyday thing for you.
[hmpf!]
Not quite.
[SEIYA] (ah!)
[MACARON] Yeah, it's more like
once every year or so.
[SEIYA] (sigh) I'm surprised
the park's made it this far.
Moff... Well, anyway I'm sorry.
Go ahead and fire me
if you want.
He's only saying that
because he knows how much
we need him around here.
[SEIYA] All right, fine.
I'll let it slide
just this once.
[BOTH] (ah!)
[SEIYA] But next time,
I'll fire you on the spot.
You got that?
Moff!
[ISUZU]
I thought he was a goner.
[SEIYA]
He's our top character.
Plus, those memory‐wiping
bullets of yours came in
pretty handy too.
[ISUZU] Oh, right, about that...
Yeah, what is it?
Well, these
Forgotten Realm Bullets
happen to be ridiculously
hard to come by.
It takes a whole year
just to make one.
They're limited, so we can't
afford to waste them.
Oh jeez, I had no idea those
things were so valuable. Wait...
What about those super‐painful
ones you keep on firing
at me and Moffle
like it's going outta style?
[ISUZU]
Those were Pain Bringers.
They cost 30 yen for a 10‐pack.
(argh!) Really?!
I'm just saying that
certain ammunition
is intended to be used
more sparingly.
All right... Anyway,
I really appreciate you
saving our butts back there.
[ISUZU] Oh, no...
Regardless of what happens,
I've already decided to do
everything in my power.
I see. Then, I may need another
body for something soon.
[hmmm?]
I didn't realize THIS
was what he meant
when he said that
he needed a body!
[OTHERS] (uhhh...)
Aren't these...
a little bit too revealing?
WTF, guys? He actually expects
us to walk around in these?
Hashtag pervert, post.
Yeah, why couldn't it be
hot guys instead?
Vrksasana is the tree pose!
Whoa there, Sylphy! You can't
do yoga with your wings on.
[pop!]
[SYLPHY] Oh!
I didn't know those
could come off!
[SYLPHY] Virabhadrasana III!
Oh yeah, they're just
part of the costume.
They are?! How can a place
with actual magic
be so full of cheap gimmicks?
Sir Kanie,
are you certain it's all right
for me to be involved with
an operation like this?
Sure, I don't mind.
Actually, I was really grateful
that you agreed to
help me out with it.
Now, get ready!
One, two, three, go!
[ALL] We're the AmaBri girls
and we're happy to say
just for 30 yen,
you can play all day.
Let me see some more energy!
Ready... go!
[ALL] We're the AmaBri girls
and we're happy to say
for just 30 yen,
you can play all day!
Latifah,
try not to look so stiff.
[SEIYA] Even more energy!
Aaand go!
[ALL] WE'RE THE AMABRI GIRLS
AND WE'RE HAPPY TO SAY,
FOR JUST 30 YEN,
YOU CAN PLAY ALL DAY!
[SEIYA] Come on, Sento,
you're not even smiling.
One more time!
[ALL on VIDEO] We're the AmaBri
girls and we're happy to say,
for just 30 yen,
you can play all day!
[TRIKEN] Oh yes, this will do,
this will do just fine!
In fact,
I'm hunched over with joy!
[SEIYA] You don't LOOK
hunched over, but great.
[TRIKEN] You know,
I was surprised Mr. Moffle
allowed Princess Latifah
to be in the video.
Huh? Wait, what do you mean?
[TRIKEN] Oh, that's right,
perhaps nobody told you.
Mr. Moffle is actually
the princess'‐
[MOFFLE] Seiya Kanieeeee!
[whomp!]
You have to stop this now!
Now what's wrong?!
[MOFFLE] That ad is obscene!
I told you,
I'm not taking orders from you!
How dare you treat my
Latifah like that?!
You little...
I'm gonna make you pay for this!
[SEIYA] Hyaaaah!
Wait, I see his pattern!
[ungh!] You're mine!
[gun fires twice]
[BOTH] (ungh...]
[ISUZU] No fighting.
[SEIYA] This feels familiar.
[ISUZU]
Try to calm down, Lord Moffle.
[MOFFLE] Calm down?
Latifah's in bad health.
She was too exposed!
I can't forgive that!
What do you mean bad health?
Besides, I told her
she didn't have to do it
if she didn't want to.
Latifah's a very sweet girl.
She doesn't know how to say no.
And you took advantage of that!
[ISUZU] Relax. Her Highness
knew what was expected of her
before she agreed.
Well, even if she did, she‐
I've told you this
several times.
Making a fuss
about things like this
will only make Her Majesty
even more miserable.
You've got a point.
But please don't take her out of
the rooftop garden anymore
if at all possible, all right?
That's her magic barrier.
[ISUZU] Of course, I know that.
Why? What happens?
[MOFFLE] (hmph!)
Why should I even bother
explaining that to you?
You'll be gone in
three months, right?
The truth is Princess Latifah
suffers from certain
complications
that make it difficult for her
to leave the magic protection
of the rooftop garden.
And is it such a big secret
that you can't even tell me
what's wrong with her?
No, not exactly.
It's just... it's not the sort
of thing a lot of people
should know about.
I don't think it'll get in
the way of your management
responsibilities,
but I do recommend that you
keep it in mind from now on.
[TRIKEN] (hmmm?)
[SEIYA] (sigh)
What do you propose we do,
Acting Manager?
Finish it like we planned.
I've got another video I
want you to edit after that,
so get this one done
as quick as you can.
[TRIKEN] Understood.
[MACARON] I gotta say,
that video's not getting
very many views so far.
[MOFFLE] Stop looking at it!
[MACARON] Okay!
[sigh] No surprise there.
Even swimsuits aren't enough
to get the public's attention
these days.
[SEIYA] Sento...
Yes?
Could you tell me the total
visitor count for today?
[ISUZU]
198, no different than normal.
Thank you.
[aha!]
So about the swimsuit video
we posted...
Well, it appears we've had
an unexpected turn of
events overnight.
[hmpf] Oh, I know.
[ISUZU] You do?
Good, then maybe we can
deal with it quickly.
Moff o' the morning!
[ISUZU] (hmmm?)
[MOFFLE] Check this out!
[TAKESHI'S DAD] (ungh)
[ISUZU]
Yes, I was just about to break
the news to Kanie, actually.
Aw, man! I'm a star mascot
no matter what I'm doing!
My charm can even turn the
stickiest of situations into
golden opportunities!
I'm so talented, I scare myself.
Say, how many hits does that
swimsuit video have now?
Last time I checked,
it was over 12,000.
But look at MY video!
Ta‐da! 200K!
Which means yours is probably
just getting attention
because it comes up as
related whenever somebody
clicks on mine!
Sure sucks to be you right now,
doesn't it?
[SEIYA] (chuckling)
What's with you?
(chuckling, into laughing)
[MOFFLE]
Wh‐what's so moffin' funny?!
Did you see who
posted the video?
[MOFFLE]
A, Y, I, E, S...
"Ayies"?
What's that s'posed to be?
[SEIYA]
Try reading it backwards.
[MOFFLE] Seiya!
[ISUZU] (gasp!)
You didn't!
Believe it or not, I did.
I was the one who
posted that video!
Right, Triken?
[TRIKEN] Right!
You see, Miss Salama captured
the footage of the fight
and then the acting manager and
I did the editing and posted it.
So, there you have it.
"Star mascot" huh?
If Triken and I hadn't
posted that video,
then nobody would've ever
found out that you did anything
in the first place!
And your charm?
If we hadn't cut it to look
like you were the good guy,
the Internet would hate your
little rat guts by now!
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
So, it looks like I'M the one
who knows how to turn
the stickiest of situations
into golden opportunities.
I'm so good I scare myself.
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
Lord Moffle's video aside,
the fact remains that
not many people have seen
the swimsuit ad yet.
Will this really
attract more people?
Even if it does,
it won't be that many.
[BOTH] (huh?)
My statistical knowledge
tells me that
fewer than 1% of the people
who saw that ad
will actually decide
to come here.
[ISUZU] Then why did you make us
wear those embarrassing
bathing suits?!
Because if it gets us one more
visitor, it's worth it!
[BOTH] Huh?!
I'm ready to do
whatever it takes.
I have to go.
The guests are waiting for me.
[sigh]
[CHILDREN]
(shouting & giggling)
Oh, good evening,
Mr. Acting Manager.
It's nice to see you.
Hey, how's today's
visitor count looking?
We managed to get
a few more today. 223!
That's great! It looks like
the changes are already
starting to pay off.
[OKURO]
Yeah, and that's not all.
[BOTH] (hmmm?)
[CHILDREN]
(shouting & giggling)
[SEIYA] Yeah?
[OKURO]
Mr. Moffle seems like he's extra
fired up today or something.
He's doing a great job.
[OKURO]
The kids look really happy.
[MOFFLE] Moff! Moff! Moff!
That's our star mascot for you.
[ISUZU]
I was told this was a party...
for boosting everyone's morale.
So why are there
only four of us?
[MOFFLE]
Nobody else wanted to come.
That's because bonding
over booze is something
old people do!
Didn't you know that?
Well, anyway,
good work today, guys! Moff...
[ALL] Cheers!
[ISUZU] Chee‐
[MACARON] Maybe you're not so
popular after all, Moffle‐ron.
[MOFFLE] (grrr)
[TIRAMY]
Yeah, some Cast Leader you are!
[MOFFLE] (ungh)
Plus, there's that
sister complex, mii.
[MOFFLE]
What are you talking about?
Everybody knows it.
The only reason you're
so protective of
Princess Latifah‐ron
is because she's the spitting
image of your sister, and you‐
[MOFFLE] (grrr!)
[BOTH] (ooowwww!)
You punks got a problem with
me caring about my niece?!
Oh, now you've done it!
You wanna piece of mii?!
[BOTH] You're goin' down!
[MOFFLE] Not today!
[guns firing]
[ISUZU] No fighting.
[OTHERS] (ow, ow, ow)
[TIRAMY] Jeez, Isuzu, a girl
should be more gentle, mii!
[ISUZU] What do I care about how
you think girls should behave?
Isuzu, you seem like
you're in a bad mood.
This is about Kanie, isn't it?
Why would you be bringing up
Kanie all of a sudden?
Well, it's just that I noticed
that every time you were
around him today,
you looked a little sad,
that's all.
Ooh, that sounds like
a scandal, mii!
That dirty dog, ron!
That was nothing.
You know, Macaron,
I heard she spent the night
over at Kanie's place
not too long ago!
Oh, really?
So they're shackin' up?!
[ISUZU] (grrr)
[guns firing]
[ALL] (ow, ow, ow)
[ISUZU] (panting)
[WANIPEE] What'll we dooooo?!
[ISUZU] (huh?)
Princess Latifah, she...
[MOFFLE] Moffu?!
[gasp]
[ISUZU & SEIYA] Time for
the attractions spotlight.
[ISUZU] Today's feature is
Tiramy's Flower Adventure.
[SEIYA] (ugh) You mean
the super‐uncomfortable
gondola ride?
[ISUZU] Apparently, Tiramy
offers a backstage tour.
[SEIYA]
What do you mean "apparently"?
Shouldn't you know
that for sure?
[ISUZU] Rumor has it the tour's
only available to attractive
female visitors.
[SEIYA] Oh, of COURSE it is!
Shut it down!