[ISUZU]
(sigh)
(relax)
(notice)
[ISUZU]
What is it?
[MACARON]
Isuzu‐ron?
Is the plan still on
for tonight?
[ISUZU]
Yes, go ahead and
proceed, please.
[MACARON]
Gotcha! See ya later.
[ISUZU]
(unsure)
(focused exhale)
[ISUZU] Good morning. hm?
[SEIYA] Perfect as usual.
[ISUZU]
Don't you get tired of
doing that every day?
[SEIYA]
Nope. not in the slightest!
[ISUZU]
Oh.
[SEIYA]
By the way...
When is the AC gonna be fixed?
[ISUZU]
Tomorrow at the earliest.
[SEIYA]
Ugh...
[ISUZU]
B‐by the way Kanie,
I wanted to give you a‐
(phone rings)
[SEIYA]
Hold that thought.
It's Kanie.
Oh, good morning.
Right now? Oh no,
it's not a problem.
I'll be right over.
Latifah says she needs
to talk to me.
[ISUZU]
Um, Kanie?
[SEIYA]
What is it?
[ISUZU]
I um... no, nevermind.
[SEIYA]
Okay. see ya.
[ISUZU]
(sigh)
(phone buzzes)
[TIRAMY]
I can't wait to see his face!
[MACARON]
It's gonna be so awesome!
[MOFFLE]
Morning‐moff.
[TIRAMY]
Morning‐mii.
[MACARON]
Morning‐ron.
What's with the tuxedo?
[MOFFLE]
PR work at Wakuwaku Preschool.
[TIRAMY]
Wakuwaku Preschool‐mii?!
[MACARON]
That's right, I forgot!
Today's the yearly visit!
[MOFFLE]
Moff... I was thinking
I'd take those three new girls
as part of their training.
[MACARON]
Hope they make it.
[TIRAMY]
If they survive,
they're ready for anything.
[MOFFLE]
Take care of everything
while I'm gone.
[MACARON/TIRAMY]
No problem!
[MOFFLE]
What about tonight?
[MACARON]
Under control.
I got catering from
a really good Italian place.
[MOFFLE]
Good!
Thanks for taking care of it.
[MUSE]
I'm sorry I made you come
all the way here, Miss Isuzu.
[ISUZU]
It's fine...
So what was the problem?
[MUSE]
Well, I slept funny...
And now my neck's twisted!
[ISUZU]
Okay... that's not good...
[OKURO]
Listen. Do you really
think I have
what it takes to do
Mr. Moffle's job?
[TIRAMY]
All you have to do is wave‐mii!
[OKURO]
Right.
Um, I think my legs are showing.
[TIRAMY]
Hmm... Eh, it's fine.
[MOFFLE] Eiko Adachi!
[EIKO] Present!
[MOFFLE] Biino Bando!
[BIINO] Present!
[MOFFLE] Shiina Chujo!
[SHIINA] D'I'm here!
[MOFFLE]
Moff... I'm glad
all three of you showed up.
[EIKO]
Excuse me, Mr. Moffle...
What exactly are we doing today?
[MOFFLE]
We're doing some off‐grounds PR
work as part of your training.
[BIINO]
PR work... off‐grounds?
[MOFFLE]
Moff. We're visiting Wakuwaku
Preschool in Amagi City.
The goal is to make a good
impression so they'll decide to
come for their fall field trip.
[SHIINA]
S‐sounds good.
[MOFFLE]
That's what I like to hear.
Get ready to‐aaaghh!
[EIKO/BIINO/SHIINA]
Hmm?
[MOFFLE]
Moff it all! I forgot something!
[SHIINA]
What was it?
They're expecting us
to bring a prize.
Bando... I think it's in the
admin room, could you grab it?
[BIINO]
Just leave it to me sir!
(dash)
[LATIFAH]
Here's the information
on the Maple Land Senate
Budgetary Committee.
[SEIYA]
Oh thanks...
I was pretty sure I told Ashe
to handle this for me though.
[LATIFAH]
Well, I know my way around
these kinds of files anyway,
so I went ahead and located it.
I wanted to be
of use to you somehow.
[SEIYA]
Hmm?
It's from Sento.
[LATIFAH]
Go on.
[SEIYA]
Sorry.
Ah jeez.
[LATIFAH]
Did something happen?
[SEIYA]
Muse twisted her neck
pretty bad last night...
So she's not gonna
be able to perform.
[LATIFAH]
Oh...
[BIINO]
(panting) Please excuse me!
Huh? Nobody's in here...
I wonder where it could be...
Oh, right there!
Gotcha!
[OKURO]
(panting) So hot...
[CHIBA]
Look mommy, I can see the man
inside the Moffle suit!
[CHIBA'S MOM]
Shush! Just pretend
you don't notice it!
[BIINO]
Sorry for the wait!
[MOFFLE]
Oh is that the prize?
[BIINO]
Yep!
Moff... smaller than I thought.
[SEIYA]
Okay, got it.
We just need someone
to replace Muse, right?
[ISUZU]
That's basically it, yes.
[SEIYA]
Here's what we'll do.
Sento's got
fairly good reflexes,
and Latifah can handle
the paperwork for a while.
[SEIYA]
Muse, you go rest up
in the garden.
[ISUZU]
Can I really pull this off?
[LATIFAH]
I‐I'll do what I can!
[MUSE]
Are you sure it's okay
for me to be
wearing this dress?
[SALAMA]
I get that we need somebody
to fill in for Muse and
Miss Isuzu but...
...doesn't the princess
just kinda sit there?
[LATIFAH]
(shock)
[MUSE]
Salama, that was rude!
[SALAMA]
(surprised)
S‐sorry princess!
[LATIFAH]
Oh no...
that's correct, actually.
I will need you to make
the croquettes though.
[LATIFAH]
Sir Nick can explain
the details.
[MUSE]
Um... okay!
[SEIYA]
That should settle it then.
[PA VOICE]
This concludes the first
performance of the day.
[PA VOICE]
We hope you enjoyed the show.
[MACARON/METAL GUYS]
(exhausted)
[MACARON]
What's up?
The catering place‐ron?
Yeah we're still planning
to do it this evening.
[MACARON]
Huh?! What do you mean
you're gonna have to cancel?!
Mass food poisoning?!
Are you kidding me‐ron?!
[MAN A]
Why's he wobbling?
[OKURO]
(heavy panting)
(collapse)
[TIRAMY]
Whoa! Did you pee‐mii?!
[OKURO]
No it's sweat, actually...
Now... let's all
welcome our guests
from Amagi Brilliant Park.
[EIKO] Hello there everybody!
[BIINO] Hey there everybody!
[SHIINA] H‐hey there everybody!
[MOFFLE] Moff!
[PRINCIPAL]
Ah, Mr. Moffle?
Those girls don't look like
they're tough enough for this.
[MOFFLE]
It'll be a good
learning experience.
[PRINCIPAL]
Alright...
[KING CRIMSON]
Hey AmaBri!
You losers better step off!
[GRAND BLUE]
Yeah, the fall field trip
is ours!
[STAY GOLD]
These kids are comin'
to Tama Kartland!
[MOFFLE]
Hmph... Stupid marsupials.
[SHIINA]
Wh‐who are those guys?
[MOFFLE]
Oh, that's the enemy team.
[EIKO/BIINO/SHIINA]
Huh?
It's time to head on over
to Wakuwaku Coliseum.
YAY!
[SEIYA]
(exert)
I need you to sort
these files.
Put everything that has to do
with Animus in its own pile.
[LATIFAH]
I think I can manage that.
[SEIYA]
Ugh. it's like an oven in here!
I hope you'll be okay.
[LATIFAH]
Oh yes... I brought a Nix
Wind Chime with me,
so I'm almost chilly.
[SEIYA] Really?
I don't feel any different.
[LATIFAH]
Oh, it isn't working?
Perhaps it doesn't affect
inhabitants of
the natural world.
[SEIYA]
Hmmm...
[LATIFAH]
Anyway, I'll watch over
the office,
so please do whatever
you need to do today.
[SEIYA]
Okay...
If you're sure, I guess I'll go.
[LATIFAH]
Of course! Take care then!
(determined)
[ISUZU]
I'm the water spirit...
Call me Muse.
Welcome to Elementario.
[DORNELL]
Your delivery is terrible.
Again.
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
(dejected)
[MUSE]
(happy sigh)
I could get used to this...
[NICK]
Hey, there you are.
I'm supposed to teach you
how to make croquettes.
[Kids]
Kick their butts! Kick their
butts! Kick their butts!
[PRINCIPAL]
Here at Wakuwaku Preschool
our policy is
"fight for what you want
and beat up anyone
who gets in your way"
so if you want that field trip,
better fight like you mean it!
[MOFFLE]
She's not kidding.
get ready for
a moffin' bloodbath.
[EIKO/BIINO/SHIINA]
(shocked)
Yep, this is what PR work
is all about.
[BIINO]
I won't let you down!
[SHIINA]
Huh?!
[MOFFLE]
You're first, Eiko!
Show those koala creeps
who's boss!
[EIKO]
O‐okay...
[PRINCIPAL]
The first round begins now!
Please welcome the
first challenger
from Amagi Brilliant Park...
Miss Eiko Adachi!
[PRINCIPAL]
And in Tama Kartland's corner...
the dreaded King Crimson!
[Kids]
(cheers escalate)
[KING CRIMSON]
(rapid drinking)
(dramatic blow)
[EIKO]
(nervous laugh)
[CAST GUY A]
Hey, you're up!
[CAST GAL A]
Hm? Okay!
[MACARON]
Yes, tonight...
I've been turned down
by 4 places now.
No wait a sec!
Can't we make a deal?
[MACARON] C'mon, be a pal‐ron...
[TIRAMY] That was a bad idea.
[OKURO]
(groan)
[KING CRIMSON]
Prepare for a world of pain!
[EIKO]
(panicking)
[BRAT C]
Anything goes!
[BRAT A]
Wahoo!
[BRAT B]
Pulverize her!
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
(realize)
(sniffing)
[BRAT A]
That girl...
[BRAT C]
From the theme park...
[BRAT B]
She's close!
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
(look)
[MOFFLE]
They like to market that red guy
as a laid‐back character.
But once he snaps
he gets pretty bloodthirsty.
[EIKO] (shriek)
[KING CRIMSON] (growling)
[SHIINA]
Uh‐oh...
[EIKO]
(squeal)
[BIINO]
Oh no! Eiko!
[PRINCIPAL] 1! 2! 3!
[KING CRIMSON] (snickering)
[EIKO]
(dazed)
[MOFFLE/BIINO/SHIINA]
(disappointed)
[LATIFAH]
This goes here...
And that goes there.
[LATIFAH]
(inhale, exhale)
That's the end of that box.
[LATIFAH]
(surprised at phone)
(reach)
[LATIFAH]
Secretary's desk?
Hm? It's about the written
estimate for the parade?
Let's see...
[ISUZU]
I'm the earth spirit... Kobory.
I hope you enjoy the show today.
[DORNELL]
That's just as bad as before.
Again!
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
(dejected)
[MUSE] Huh?
[NICK] First I need you to mince
all these onions.
[MUSE]
This whole box? by myself?
[NICK]
Princess Latifah
never has trouble with it.
[MUSE]
(panic)
[TRIKEN]
Please proceed according to
the schedule I sent.
[TRIKEN]
Yes, I'm bowing with‐
[OFFICE GUY A]
Product samples are here.
[SEIYA]
(startled)
[ASHE]
This is accounting.
Of course, give me one moment.
I'm pulling that
invoice for you.
Ah yes, this is the one...
Right, the payment
hasn't been processed yet.
[ASHE]
Yes... Have a great day.
[CHIEF GEN]
Excuse me sir,
I need to get something from
that drawer if you don't mind.
[SEIYA]
Sure.
[CHIEF GEN]
One second please.
Thank you.
[SEIYA]
Mm‐hm.
[Kids]
(screaming, cheering)
[PRINCIPAL]
Moving on to round two!
Biino Bando versus Grand Blue!
[GRAND BLUE]
I'm gonna eat you alive!
[BIINO] (scream)
[MOFFLE]
The blue koala supposedly has
a relaxed personality,
but once that moffer
loses his temper it's all over.
[BIINO] (scream)
[GRAND BLUE] Haahahahahahah!
[SHIINA]
But that's exactly the same
as the first one!
[MOFFLE]
True. Except...
[GRAND BLUE]
You've got nowhere to run,
you little rat!
[BIINO] (weak)
[GRAND BLUE] (confused)
[BIINO] Ow, that hurt...
[GRAND BLUE]
(shock)
(dramatic collapse)
[GRAND BLUE]
(dazed)
[MOFFLE]
...the guy's terrified of blood.
[PRINCIPAL]
Grand Blue down!
Biino Bando wins!
[BIINO]
(surprised)
Yayyyy!
Look everybody! I did it!
[MOFFLE]
All's well that ends well.
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
(look)
[BRAT C]
A clock?
[BRAT A]
That's stupid.
[BRAT B]
Hey... how 'bout this?
[BRAT C/BRAT A]
(snicker)
[MACARON]
Please, you're my last
option‐ron!
[MACARON]
I'll throw in a little extra‐
(surprised) Agh...DAMMIT!
[LATIFAH]
I see, so you'd like to change
tomorrow's meeting from 1 to 3?
[TRIKEN]
Excuse me, I'm here about
the advertisement schedule‐
[TRIKEN]
Princess Latifah?
[LATIFAH]
(startled) I'm so sorry!
Um, just a minute please!
[WRENCH]
Hey missy, I need a signature
for the‐ what's with the line?
Let's see, according
to the calendar,
it seems Sir Kanie‐
[TRIKEN] Hunch over and wait.
[WRENCH] Huh?
[LATIFAH]
Yes... Yes...
Oh, you have two
separate meetings?
[ISUZU]
Spirit of the wind...
I'm Sylphy.
Want to be friends?
[DORNELL]
That was the worst yet! Again!
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
(dejected)
[MUSE] (sigh)
[NICK] You done with the onions?
[MUSE]
Ah, yes!
[MUSE] Huh?
Now peel all the
potatoes in this box.
[MUSE] (panicking)
All this? Myself?!
[NICK]
Princess Latifah never
has trouble with it.
[SALESGUY A]
I'm from Marukawa.
Where should I put all these
key holders you guys ordered?
[MER] (cartoonish gesturing)
[SALESGUY A] Got it.
[SALESGUY B]
Hey I'm from Hinode Sewing.
Is there a certain place
you'd like me to put the
Moffle, Macaron
and Tiramy dolls?
[MER] (more gesturing)
[SALESGUY B] Got it.
[SALESGUY C]
I'm from Amagi Transport.
Could you sign
for these, please?
[SALESGUY D]
Excuse me sir,
but the unloading area's full.
Where would you like me
to put these?
Oh, I can just
leave 'em right here?
Okay thanks, have a good day.
[SALESGUY E]
Sorry to interrupt you sir,
but can I leave these here too?
Perfect. thanks a lot.
[SEIYA]
(annoyed)
[PRINCIPAL]
It's time for the final round!
Shiina Chujo versus Stay Gold!
[STAY GOLD]
I'll crush your bones to dust!
[SHIINA] Noooo!
[MOFFLE]
Looks like his personality's
a little different
than the other two, but yeah,
it's basically the same deal
whenever he gets angry.
[BIINO]
I'll remember that, sir!
[EIKO]
I wasn't aware it was acceptable
to attack your opponent
with a chain.
[SHIINA] (scream)
[STAY GOLD] Hraggghhh!
Moff, who cares as long
as she wins?
[BIINO]
Good thinking, sir!
[STAY GOLD]
You're mine, kid!
[SHIINA]
Huh?
[STAY GOLD]
(stunned)
[Kids]
(berserk cheers)
There it is!
The winner is Shiina Chujo!
[PRINCIPAL]
Amagi Brilliant Park wins 2‐1!
[BRAT A/BRAT B/BRAT C]
(sinister laughing)
[PRINCIPAL]
You put up a spectacular
fight, AmaBri.
[KING CRIMSON]
(grunt)
We'll be seeing you in the fall.
[MOFFLE]
Thank you.
You also get
both of the prizes...
Thank you again
for coming today.
[MOFFLE]
I appreciate that.
[SHIINA]
B‐b‐but I thought those p‐prizes
were f‐for the p‐preschoolers!
[MOFFLE]
Would you have come
if you had known?
[LATIFAH]
U‐unfortunately
the person in charge isn't
available that day...
...so I don't believe
we'll be able to, um...
[ASHE]
(gasp)Your Highness!
[LATIFAH]
Oh! Lady Ashe!
I'm so sorry
to keep you waiting!
[ASHE]
Um, do you need some help?
[LATIFAH]
Y‐yes, if you don't mind!
Thank you very much!
[ISUZU]
I'm the fire spirit... Salama.
I like internet flame wars...?
[DORNELL]
Why are you so bad?!
Start over from the top!
[ISUZU]
(surprised)
(dejected)
[KOBORY]
But it's well into
the evening by now.
[SALAMA]
Welp! Guess we're not
performing today.
[SYLPHY]
Caspian Sea Monster!
[SEIYA]
(annoyed) Jeez.
(approaching footsteps)
[SEIYA]
Huh?
[TIRAMY]
(unwell "mii")
(straining mii"s)
MIIIII!
[SEIYA]
(big horrified)
(relieved "mii")
(disgusted)
(annoyed)
[MUSE]
Ugh... she's way tougher
than I thought.
How does she do this
by herself?!
[MOFFLE]
Moff, you're dismissed.
Bando, could you go put
the prizes in the admin room?
[BIINO]
Sure!
[LATIFAH]
Whew...
I finally finished it...
I'd better go report
to Sir Kanie now.
[BIINO]
(running up steps)
Oh Princess!
[LATIFAH]
Hello there,
I was just going out...
Shall I leave this door open?
[BIINO]
Sure. I'll close it
when I get done.
[LATIFAH]
Excellent. take care then.
[BIINO]
Thanks; you too!(run over)
Whew, there we go.(run out)
[MOFFLE]
Hey there Seiya,
what are you up to?
[SEIYA]
Working. The AC's broken
in the admin room.
[MOFFLE]
Moff... Well just so you know,
we got the preschool field trip.
[SEIYA]
Really? That's good to hear!
[MOFFLE]
It was all thanks to those
three new part‐timers...
Make sure you tell them thanks.
Sure thing. thanks for
your help today.
[MOFFLE]
Moff.
[ISUZU/LATIFAH/MUSE]
Good work, everyone.
[LATIFAH]
(giggling)
[MUSE/ISUZU]
(hm?)
(smile, into giggle)
[MUSE]
We should probably stick
to what we do best from now on.
[ISUZU]
I agree with that.
[LATIFAH]
(giggle)
Oh that's right,
is your neck feeling better?
[MUSE]
Yeah, I'm totally fine now.
Thanks for asking.
[ISUZU]
Ah... So the preschool visit
turned out to be a success.
[ISUZU]
(inhale‐exhale)
[SEIYA]
(big stretch)
[LATIFAH] Sir Kanie?
[SEIYA] Hm?
I don't suppose you could
spare a brief moment?
[SEIYA]
I guess... What do you need?
[ISUZU]
You'll have to see for yourself.
[ALL]
Happy Birthday!
Thanks for all you do!
[SEIYA]
(stunned)
Huh...?
[MACARON]
Ha! check it out!
he's so surprised
he can't even talk straight!
[MOFFLE]
The ambush mission
was a success!
[TIRAMY]
He's crying‐mii!
[SEIYA]
N‐no I'm not! don't be stupid!
(unsure)
W‐well, I guess I
should probably thank you
knuckleheads...
[LATIFAH/ISUZU]
(giggling)
[SEIYA]
Did you know about this too?
[LATIFAH]
Yes, I'm sorry...
Everyone asked me to keep it
secret. I had no choice.
[LATIFAH]
Like it or not,
we're here to celebrate
your birthday, Sir Kanie!
[ALL] Yeah!
[SEIYA] (startled)
[SEIYA]
(slurp)
Hmm... not bad.
(giggle)
Why are we having
somen noodles‐mii?
[MACARON]
It's the only thing I could get.
[ISUZU]
Her Majesty has retired
for the night.
[SEIYA]
That's good.
You know, that really
did surprise me.
I've never had a birthday party
like that in my whole life.
You really haven't?
[SEIYA]
Those guys are way too busy
to put something
like this together.
What am I gonna do with them?
[ISUZU]
(smile)
[SEIYA]
Check out what Latifah gave me.
They're some kind of
scented candles.
[ISUZU]
Oh.
[ISUZU] Actually...
[SEIYA] Hm?
[ISUZU]
I‐I got you a present too.
So, um... you know...
[SEIYA]
Huh?
[ISUZU]
It's not much, but... I...
I just thought it...
kind of suited you...
[SEIYA]
(speechless)
[ISUZU]
So if you wouldn't mind...
I... I want you to have it.
[SEIYA]
Um, okay...
[ISUZU]
Well... goodnight!
[SEIYA]
(surprised)
(stunned)
[SEIYA]
Hm?!
(stunned)
[SEIYA]
Cicada shells?