[MAKISE gasps]
[OKABE whimpers]
[sighs] Jeez, thanks for
letting me know you were here.
You're going to get arrested
creeping around like that.
[faucet squeaks]
Oh, Happy New Year, I guess.
That's the part where
you're supposed to say it back.
Or maybe it's already too late
to wish people Happy New Year?
Anyway... I'm
shocked to see you.
You never show
your face these days.
[gasps]
Hey! Can we not
start the year like this?
[OKABE whimpers]
[sobbing]
[OKABE]
Apologies.
Don't worry about it.
Happens to me
sometimes, too.
Were you thinking of her?
Mayuri, I mean.
Huh?
I can't come here without
the memories flooding in.
I hear her footsteps,
then the door opens,
and I half expect to hear
her little sing-song greeting.
--[cup clatters]
--[MAKISE gasps]
Okabe?
[OKABE whimpering]
Are you all right?
[OKABE panting]
[gags]
[OKABE retches]
[MAKISE gasps]
Okabe?
[OKABE]
How humiliating.
[MAKISE]
Please, it's fine.
I really should have known
better. It's too soon.
Now that I think about it,
you haven't even
set foot in this place.
Not once since everything
happened with Mayuri.
[OKABE]
Guess not.
You essentially
just disappeared,
not that I blame you.
Hashida did, too,
but not on
the same level as you.
[OKABE]
How did this happen?
I'm back in
an alpha world line.
[gasps]
Where is the Phone Wave?
Asks the person
who demolished it.
You don't recall?
[MAKISE gasps]
--Okabe?
--Forgive me.
I need a little fresh air.
Sure.
I understand.
[door latch clacks]
[OKABE] The city and its people
feel exactly the same.
To them,
today's just like yesterday.
[OKABE] And yet,
in this alpha world line,
life has no meaning.
'Cause no matter what I do,
convergence will always
result in Mayuri's death.
I'm powerless.
[DARU] They're taking her
to the hospital now.
The paramedics say
it looks like a heart attack.
[OKABE] Even if we could escape
the grasp of SERN somehow,
as long as I'm
in this world line,
Mayuri's life simply
cannot be saved.
I knew that,
which is why I--
[OKABE pants]
How?! How could I
end up back here?
What made
Reading Steiner kick in?
There was no D-mail!
There was no time leaping,
so why?!
[inaudible]
--[DARU] Okarin?
--Huh?
[OKABE]
Daru?
You in Akiba?
That's a rare sight these days.
[FUBUKI]
Welcome to May Queen, meow!
Thanks for coming in, Masters!
Daddy's back!
Special treat: I brought
Okarin in with me today!
[RUKA gasps]
What? Okabe's here?
-[OKABE] Rukako?
-Kyouma!
[FARIS giggling]
[FARIS]
I've missed you so much, meow!
[OKABE] Has it really been
that long since I came in?
[RUKA]
Yeah, it has.
[DARU]
For a little while there,
I didn't come in
all that much, either.
-[FUBUKI] Excuse me.
-[GROUP] Hmm?
[FUBUKI]
My name's Fubuki.
Glad to finally meet you.
Mayuri and I
were cosplay friends,
and I just want you to know
that she meant the world to me.
[FARIS] Fubu-meow
graciously stepped in
to help out at May Queen
after our sweet
Mayushii left us.
[FUBUKI]
It's been hard for me,
but I know that Mayuri
would have wanted me
to be around other people
who loved her.
Here's a picture of us
at Summer ComiMa.
The outfits she made us
were so cute.
We took this picture,
so we could remember it forever.
She was always so energetic.
[voice breaking] And she seemed
healthy, so I was shocked.
One minute she was alive,
and the next--
[crying]
Fubu-meow. Remember what I said?
Mayushii would want you to smile
when you remember her, not cry.
Okay? I know it hurts.
[OKABE]
What if...
What if there was a world
where Mayuri was still alive?
If you knew it existed...
...would it hurt less?
[OKABE]
Daru?
[DARU firmly]
Step outside with me.
[OKABE]
H-Hey!
Poor Okabe.
[OKABE]
What is with you?
[DARU]
There are things you should say,
and things you should
definitely not say!
You want to talk about a world
where Mayuri's alive?
You're the one who
couldn't make the choice
to keep her with us in this one!
We had Echelon's data hacked.
Cracked wide open.
But you
couldn't pull the trigger!
You mean I couldn't
press the "enter" key?
[DARU]
Yeah.
And then you wouldn't
shut up about it.
You kept saying,
"I'm the one who killed her.
I did it. I killed Mayuri."
You made the choice that
effectively ended Mayuri's life.
[DARU]
And then, to top it off,
you destroyed the Phone Wave
and Time Leap Machine?
If you knew you were
going to regret it later,
you should have thought
about that and kept it intact!
Just like Miss Makise
begged you to.
[OKABE]
Kurisu did?
[DARU] She thought
we had another chance!
We could have
tried it all again!
There must have been
something we hadn't thought of!
[phone buzzes]
[MAKISE]
Hello, this is Makise.
Oh, Hashida.
It's been a while.
Happy New Year, by the way.
[DARU]
Yeah, Happy New Year and stuff.
[MAKISE]
This is a surprise.
What's going on?
You practically never call me.
I saw Okarin in Akiba.
Oh?
[DARU] I'm guessing he came
to the lab, too, didn't he?
'Course. Did he say
anything strange?
Yeah.
He still isn't over
Mayushii's death.
And then he just started
raving about another world
where she could
somehow be alive.
What'd you say?
[DARU sighs]
I got pissed.
I-I couldn't believe he'd have
the balls to say all that
after everything that happened.
You don't think he's...?
[door clicks]
[footsteps running]
[footsteps approaching]
[OKABE]
Kurisu?
How did you know I was here?
No offense.
You're predictable, so...
That's true.
--[MAKISE] Just kidding.
--Huh?
GPS.
You mean you were tracking me?
That confirms my suspicion.
Look, Okabe, be honest.
You came from a different
world line, didn't you?
[gasps]
You realize that spot
you're occupying
is the place Mayuri
always used to sit, right?
If you were the Okabe
who gave up on her,
you wouldn't ever dream
of sitting in her favorite seat.
He never did.
It's how he coped
with the guilt.
Also, you seem to have
no recollection of the GPS.
[OKABE]
You're right. So what's it for?
I won't say.
[OKABE]
It's still here?!
[MAKISE]
No, I rebuilt it.
I christened it
"Phone Wave Revised."
Although, you think "reboot"
would be more precise? Huh?
[OKABE]
You really remade it?
What for?!
To send a message into the past.
No.
In order to change world lines.
--[OKABE gasps]
--[MAKISE] Okabe.
I want you to use it.
Go back to the world line
you came from.
[OKABE]
What are you...?
In that place,
Mayuri still lives.
Or, rather, in that world line,
you were able
to find the resolve
it took to keep her alive.
[OKABE gasps]
I should have known.
--You see right through me.
--[MAKISE] Naturally.
I've watched you for so long.
No, wait.
I didn't mean in that way.
Well, that, too, but still.
That's not the point.
You're the Okabe Rintaro from
a wholly different world line.
That's all there is to say.
Go back.
I did change world lines, yes,
and in the other one,
Mayuri is still alive.
And yet...
...that other world where
Mayuri's thriving and happy,
was altered enough
to bring me back to this one,
and I've no idea how.
I wish I did.
I wish I could take
responsibility for it.
I'm powerless.
I don't know
how I ended up here.
And you, you're not there.
You loved me,
and I tried to save you.
But I failed,
and it cost you your life.
And now...
...you want me to...
You want to make me
kill you all over again?
I can't do it.
I don't have the strength.
[footsteps]
Hashida?
Where's Okarin?
[MAKISE]
Not sure. He'll be back.
I should have known.
We both should have.
Okabe never could
have let Mayuri go.
Hey, Miss Makise?
No, it's nothing.
Forget about it.
♪
[phone buzzes]
[MAKISE]
Have you made up your mind?
[OKABE sighs]
No, of course you haven't.
Well, the trains are running,
are they not?
Meet me in an hour at Akihabara
station, if you would.
What's up?
[MAKISE] There's something
I think you need to see.
[MAKISE] You're hard
to spot without the lab coat.
What is this?
Where are we going?
You'll know
when we arrive there.
--What is it?
--Oh.
I was just noting that
we've never traveled together.
Not like this.
Well, you better stop ogling me
or I shall be forced
to report you.
But I'm blameless.
The law is quite clear
on this matter.
An unwanted gaze
is sexual harassment.
[laughs softly]
Amadeus has got nothing
on the real you.
[MAKISE gasps]
Amadeus?
[OKABE] You know,
the artificial intelligence.
How did you
even hear about that?
I'm sure I never told you!
[OKABE] You're right. Hiyajo
and Professor Leskinen did.
[MAKISE gasps]
You've met Miss Maho?!
What kind of world line
would allow for that to happen?
[OKABE]
What're you so angry about?
[MAKISE]
Who says I'm angry?!
[OKABE]
Next thing we knew,
she wasn't able to access
Amadeus at all.
[MAKISE]
Hmm.
What happened to it
in this world line?
I don't know.
From a purely
logical perspective,
I can't imagine
an AI could have
much to do
with a world line change.
It doesn't make sense.
What then? Fluke?
Well, all of my memories
are contained
within the program's database.
So, it follows that
my time machine concept
would be stored therein,
as well.
-[OKABE] Wait, it would?
-[MAKISE] In theory.
Although I still denied their
plausibility at that point.
No, time machines
aren't possible.
However...
...that isn't to say that time
travel is altogether impossible.
[OKABE] Amadeus Kurisu
gave me a very different answer.
Look, please,
I just want you to read this.
'Kay, Dad?
Hold on, excuse me?
That's called stealing,
you know!
--[MAKISE] Okabe?
--[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE stammers]
I'm all right.
I admit, I struggle
to wrap my head around
your alleged friendship
with Miss Maho.
I bumped into her at a seminar.
I don't suppose
I have to tell you
just how coarse and stubborn
Hiyajo can be.
Ungainly, too.
I'm well-acquainted
with those qualities.
So, I assume you were
her feisty side-kick, then?
How rude.
I was anything but feisty
when it came to her.
I'd go so far as to
call myself courteous.
Maho adored me.
[OKABE]
Hmph.
[gasps]
[OKABE whimpers]
[whimpers]
[MAKISE] The others
must be visiting, too.
You were a wreck
after Mayuri died.
We were all very
concerned about you.
You stopped going to the lab,
you dropped out of college,
and you just stood here,
every day, sun up to sun down.
It was like...
...you were waiting
for someone to take you
to the other side.
[MAKISE] And there was
nothing I could do
to help or to make it better.
After all...
...I was the reason
that you didn't save her.
Kurisu...
[MAKISE]
Anyway, that's all over.
[MAKISE] It ends now,
because it has to.
If not, you'll live the rest of
your life crushed by the guilt.
You're mistaken.
Even if I did go back
to a beta world line...
...I'm crushed
by guilt there, too.
The feeling never leaves me,
and you're dead!
Get ahold of yourself,
Okabe Rintaro!
Please stop making that face.
[MAKISE] If Hououin Kyouma
is still in there somewhere,
then find him. Be brash
and indomitable again!
That was an act.
A dumb facade.
A lie!
It was just something
I used to do
because it always
made Mayuri happy.
And it worked. You never had
any trouble making her smile.
That's all that matters.
In the beta world line,
she is happy.
Your choice was based
on what you knew then--
It wasn't wrong.
This world line shouldn't
exist in the first place.
I shouldn't be here.
--This world is only a dream.
--[OKABE sobbing]
A bleak fantasy.
That's why you've got
to go back, Okabe.
It's a dream.
--And you have to wake up.
--A dream?
[MAKISE]
Yes.
[OKABE gasps]
♪
[MAKISE] We should
head back to the lab now.
[keyboard clacking]
[MAKISE]
Before you send the message,
I need you to make me a promise.
[OKABE]
What's that?
[MAKISE]
When you get back,
I want you to forget
all about me.
[OKABE]
I can't do that.
There's no way.
[MAKISE]
Then just promise me you'll try.
Even if it's not possible.
Sentiment aside,
Amadeus could be key.
I don't have
the slightest inkling
of what caused
your world line to change.
However, time travel had to
have been involved somehow.
[OKABE]
But the Phone Wave was--
I can't make any claims
about myself in your world line.
But in this one, there's
no question, whatsoever,
that I only completed my time
machine theory after I met you.
I can't guarantee
it won't happen again.
It would behoove you,
not to interact with Amadeus
too much when you get there.
[OKABE sighs]
This is a pinky promise.
Break it
and I'll stab an electrode
into your hippocampus!
'Cause it's a pinky promise!
--That was really lame.
--Oh, shut up.
--[MAKISE] Hey.
--Huh?
[MAKISE]
Do you remember...
...what happened
the day we first met?
You were pulling
and pawing at my clothes
like a crazy person.
I was sure you were
some kind of deranged pervert.
[OKABE]
Makes sense.
From her perspective,
that is the first time we met.
And yet, from mine, she was...
Wait!
[inaudible]
[keyboard clacking]
Everything's ready now.
All you have to do
is send that message,
and then you'll return
to the world line you came from.
[whirring]
Okabe?
Sorry. Yeah.
[OKABE]
If I send this...
...I'll be sent back,
and everything reverts.
[OKABE]
A world where Mayuri lives.
A world where
I don't have to lose her.
But instead,
I lose the woman in front of me.
Kurisu will be gone,
because I'll have killed her.
The one I love.
My most precious--
[gasps]
Okabe?
♪
[MAKISE]
I'm so grateful that I met you.
[OKABE]
Kurisu?
[groaning]
[MAKISE panting]
[inaudible]
[panting]
[gasps]
[MAKISE]
Okabe!
You should know by now!
I'm in love with--