[rain pouring]
[pencil scraping]
[OKABE sighs]
[phone vibrates]
[chuckles]
[OKABE panting]
[Daru]
Suzuha!
Oh, it's you, Dad.
Just what in the hell
are you doing
still out in this downpour?
[OKABE] It's been several months
since Kagari vanished.
We tried everything
we could to track her down.
Any means necessary, but alas.
[OKABE] In the end, there was
just no trace of her anywhere.
As for the facility
Moeka and I found,
we never uncovered
its exact purpose.
She was brainwashed?
Are you kidding me?
[DARU] We don't have
definitive proof, though.
[SUZUHA gasps]
[OKABE] We couldn't reveal
the truth about Kagari's past.
So, enlisting the help of the
authorities seemed pointless.
[rain falling]
[MAYURI]
Okarin!
[OKABE]
Mayuri?
Are you gonna be okay, silly?
[OKABE]
Huh?
I was just wondering
if you brought an umbrella.
This rain comes out of nowhere.
It sure does seem
that way lately.
[MAYURI]
Because it's the rainy season.
That's how it always is.
Of course.
It's going to
be summer pretty soon.
Oh, yeah. Right. Huh?
[MAYURI]
I love summer.
[OKABE]
Yeah.
[mouse clicks]
Uh. Hey, hot stuff!
--You're lookin' sexy.
--[MAHO yawns]
[MAHO]
Good morning.
Hiyajo. Hi. How's it goin'?
[MAHO groans]
[DARU]
A sleepy Mini Maho?
That's effing hot!
[MAHO moans]
So, I'm assuming you guys
still haven't given up,
since you're
contacting me again.
Of course we haven't!
Like I already told you,
if we end up not being able
to use the actual time machine,
then we'll be forced to recreate
the time leap machine!
And you really think
that's possible?
[DARU]
I was almost able to finish it
before Okarin freaked out
and trashed the thing,
so, yeah, I do.
But it's not even close
to being stable.
--I'm not surprised.
--[keyboard clacking]
How'd they compress
such an absurd amount of data
in order to send it
into the past?
Until you answer that question,
it seems pointless.
Why do you think we're asking
for your help again?
Because we need your mind.
Since we can't
ask Okarin anymore,
you're our only hope.
[MAHO]
Don't assume I can do anything
because I'm a scientist.
That's fallacious.
Makise Kurisu did it before.
You had a veritable genius
working on it.
[Daru] Yeah, but... I think
you're as much of a genius
in your own right,
Mini Maho.
[MAHO growls]
Spare me the flattery, please.
Look, I've got
my own work to do.
I take it the answer
is no, then?
[MAHO]
I'm hanging up now.
[Maho] Salieri couldn't compose
the symphonies Mozart did.
[MAHO]
Hmm?
[gasps]
--[MAHO screams]
--[MAN gasps]
No way.
I let them see me
in this state?!
[whimpers]
[DARU]
For real.
I feel kinda bad about this.
If Okarin found out,
he'd flip his lid.
[SUZUHA] You wanna ask him
for permission?
[DARU]
He'd say no!
As soon as he hears
what we're up to,
then it's all over.
[SUZUHA]
Exactly.
[DARU]
But you know,
Okarin always seems dead serious
when he talks about it.
He says to not even think
about changing the future.
And knowing him,
I'm sure he's got
a damn good reason
for not wanting that.
I get it.
Of all people, I understand
where he's coming from.
But still, is what
he fears worse
than letting this timeline
lead the planet
into World War Three?
I doubt it. Can't be.
[DARU] And he would probably
agree with you
at the end of the day.
[SUZUHA scoffs]
If that's true,
then why won't
he take action?
He's got everything he needs!
The time machine that
could get him to Steins Gate,
and he still has
the ability to remember
all those other world lines
by Reading Steiner.
So why has he given up on it?
Why won't he at least
try to change things?
Tell me!
[DARU] I don't think
he's given up completely.
Someday, Hououin Kyouma
will rise again
and go "mwaahahahaha"
like before.
[SUZUHA] You've been saying
that for so long.
It's been six months.
[DARU]
Well, yeah, but still.
[SUZUHA] We can't count
on Uncle Okarin anymore.
It's time to take matters
into our own hands.
[DARU]
Sorry.
I said you could count on me
and look where that landed us.
No.
Trust that I've noticed how hard
you've been pushing yourself,
and all for my sake.
[phone vibrates]
Got a text from Mayushii.
[gasps]
Something wrong?
[DARU]
It's Fubuki.
She's back in the hospital!
[gasps]
[DARU] Okay.
I'm gonna check this out.
[SUZUHA]
You'll probably see Mom there.
Good luck with that.
[DARU] You really think
I should be hitting on her now?
Sorry.
Sometimes I just get
a little freaked out
that I won't ever be conceived.
[DARU] Right! I solemnly swear
I won't let you down!
[SUZUHA]
Thanks, Dad. See you later.
[DARU]
Yes, ma'am!
I vow to do my best!
[sighs]
[SUZUHA]
Hmm?
What's that?
[footsteps]
[MAYURI gasps]
Uh?
Mayushii. Okarin came too.
Hey, Fubuki!
I'm so sorry you're here!
--Well, uh, see...
--[MAYURI, OKABE] Hmm?
I'm actually fine.
Funny story, though.
[FUBUKI] They just asked me
to check in to the hospital
so they could run
a few more tests.
But then Kaede here panicked.
Well, Fubuki said she
was gonna be hospitalized
for a little while,
and I got nervous.
I said, "for a little while,"
didn't I? Come on.
So, you're healthy.
There's no cause for concern.
Thank goodness.
--[DARU] Okarin! Mayushii!
--[YUKI gasps]
Daru?
How sweet of you
to show you care!
[DARU]
Yo, what's up, kids?
--[YUKI] Hey, Hashida.
--[DARU gasps]
[YUKI]
How are you?
Uh... Oh, hello.
Uh, Milady.
[YUKI giggles]
[DARU]
Hold on.
Fubuki, didn't you collapse?
[FUBUKI]
Jeez, they got to you, too?
[HOSPITAL DIRECTOR]
And why does everyone require
their own private room, exactly?
[ALEXIS] I'm telling you,
we require it--trust me.
That's what you keep saying,
and yet you won't justify it.
Please, sir, find a way
to make it happen!
[OKABE]
Professor Leskinen?
[HOSPITAL DIRECTOR]
Hmm?
It's been forever!
Ha, Rintaro!
[OKABE]
Wait, no, no, please, don't--!
[ALEXIS laughing]
[HOSPITAL DIRECTOR]
Professor?
You know this young man?
Yes!
This kid is the world's
third Einstein!
Rintaro here is going
to be transferring
to my university
in September,
and eventually I'm going
to bring him onboard
as part of my research team!
[HOSPITAL DIRECTOR]
Oh.
He'll be going
to Viktor Chondria?
[OKABE] Not yet. That's
my ultimate goal...
[DARU]
Hey, Mayushii, question.
Okarin's transferring overseas?
I don't think the whole
thing's set in stone yet.
But Okarin's been doing
his best and working hard!
I see.
[OKABE]
Um, the hospital director?
You'd lie to someone
so high up?
[ALEXIS]
I didn't lie to anyone, Rintaro.
I said that you were
transferring in September.
But I didn't say
of which year, now, did I?
--[chuckles]
--[OKABE sighs]
Uh, is Hiyajo in Japan, too?
[ALEXIS]
Curious, are we?
Well. I mean, yeah.
[sighs]
Unfortunately,
she remained back in America.
But rest assured,
I will tell her
that you were asking
after her, Rintaro.
Take care of yourself! Heh.
[MAHO]
Honestly,
the only reasonable
assumption here
is that they sent
the data to a third party
to be compressed.
[MAHO]
Considering most of the places
Kurisu would have reached
out to for help with that...
[OKABE] And if you make
one wrong move,
you could disgrace that legacy.
You'd be trampling her memory.
[MAHO]
"One wrong move,"
and this might turn out
the same way.
--[phone vibrating]
--Hmm?
[MAHO]
Professor?
[gasps]
[MAHO]
That's Okabe!
What the heck?!
[groans]
[AMADEUS]
Is something juicy going on?
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
The professor's
in Japan right now.
I guess he must've
run into Okabe somewhere.
Are you wishing
you'd gone with him?
No, why?
Oh. Whoa, your eyes
are really bloodshot.
'Cause I'm tired!
[AMADEUS] Okabe's such
a strange guy, though,
don't you agree?
Strange how?
Full disclosure, I thought
so from the beginning.
I mean, he asked me
straight away
if I thought it was possible
to build a time machine.
[MAHO]
Hmm?
[OKABE] Do you think one could
construct a time machine?
Uh, hello?
Hey, um, you have
Makise Kurisu's
memories from last spring,
before she went to Japan.
I mean, they're all stored
in there somewhere, aren't they?
Yeah, of course.
But why are you
randomly asking for them?
It's just--
Suppose you could--
What if someone
did find a way
to make a time machine
after all?
Are you serious?
If everything you needed
was somehow
right in front of you,
what, then?
Come on. That's foolish.
I think you know my answer.
--[MAHO] And what if...
--Uh!
...the one person
who could make it reality,
says only this:
"Time machines are
the work of pure evil.
They must never
be made or used. Ever."
[AMADEUS]
Hmm.
I don't know.
I would be hesitant.
After all,
interfering with the past
seems so risky.
What would become of those
of us in the present?
We don't have
the slightest idea.
[MAHO]
Yeah, you're right.
[AMADEUS]
Although...
To be honest,
I'd probably still build it.
Would I ever use it?
That's the conundrum.
[SUZUHA]
Could she have dropped this?
Half a year ago?
No. There's no way.
She must have come by here.
[phone vibrates]
[sighs]
[SUZUHA] I think I'm gonna
take a hot shower.
[shower curtain scrapes]
[water running]
[door unlocks]
[SUZUHA humming]
[SUZUHA]
♪ La, la, la... ♪
[singing continues]
[SUZUHA]
Not another move.
If you try anything funny,
I'll shoot you.
Put your hands on your head.
And walk slowly
towards the door.
[song continues]
That's far enough.
[SUZUHA]
Isn't it a little hot
for you to be wearing
that outfit?
Why don't you take
off your helmet?
Get some fresh air.
[gasps]
[SUZUHA gasping]
[SUZUHA]
Kagari?
[KAGARI]
He talks to me.
I hear the voice of God.
Why, Kagari?
What have you done with it?
My precious gift.
The one Mommy gave me.
Please, listen.
You have it, don't you?
It's mine!
[grunting]
[KAGARI gasps]
It's hard to believe
you're the same girl.
The little princess who always
cried in the time machine.
I'm impressed.
[KAGARI gasping]
[SUZUHA]
Your mommy...
You made her cry.
Mommy cried...?
[gasps]
Uh!
[KAGARI yelps]
[thuds]
[BOTH grunting]
[KAGARI gasping]
Now if you behave yourself,
I won't have to kill you.
[KAGARI]
Suzuha.
It hurts!
You're hurting me.
Please, stop it!
My arm! [sobs]
[DARU]
Suzuha, what's going on?
Why'd you leave
the door wide open?
[ALL gasp]
[grunting]
Dad, watch out! The knife!
[DARU whimpers]
[SUZUHA]
Kagari!
Go ahead.
Try to hurt my dad
if you wanna die.
I don't care who you are.
I will not hesitate!
Uh? [yelps]
Come back here!
[DARU panting]
What happened?
That was Kagari,
but different.
Yeah.
Why would she
ever act that way?
[DARU]
Suzuha, did you notice?
[DARU] I'm pretty sure
Kagari was crying.
[gasping]
[SUZUHA]
Ow!
Oh, crap, I'm sorry.
Are you sure we shouldn't
take you to the hospital?
I'm fine.
Just a scratch, I'll make it.
[DARU] So, the woman
in the motorcycle suit
was Kagari all along.
It wasn't.
The person who
attacked you guys,
that was someone else.
At the time of the incident,
Kagari was still
at the shrine.
[DARU]
Then, who?
Not sure,
but I am willing to bet
that Uncle Okarin's theory
was right in the end.
Kagari actually
was brainwashed,
and whoever did it
is still controlling her now.
But who'd do that? And why?
Twelve years ago,
someone dangerous
must've found out
that she came here
in a time machine,
and so, they captured her.
[gasps]
What's the matter?
[KAGARI]
He talks to me.
I hear the voice of God.
[KAGARI]
I hear... a voice...
The "voice of God."
--But who--?
--Huh?
It can't be!
Does that mean
that when we left,
she was already...?
Hold on.
I just think I should
let Okarin know.
He'd want me to tell him
Kagari showed up.
Yeah, but think about it.
If he hears
that Kagari is back,
he might become obsessed
with trying to find her again,
and that won't help us.
I mean, consider
what you just witnessed.
Kagari is dangerous.
She's unstable.
And besides,
if Kagari was brainwashed,
I think I know a way
we can undo the damage.
We can get her back.
Although, in order
to save her,
as dangerous
as it would be,
we'll probably have to use
the time machine.
[SUZUHA]
I am such an idiot!
Why did it take me
so long to remember?
That bastard tormented
my Valkyrie comrades
one after the other.
The man from the Bureau...
The professor!
Suzuha...
[sighs]
[SUZUHA]
What, Dad?
[DARU] I'm gonna reach out
to Maho again.
Huh?
[DARU] I want to ask her
to come back to Japan
and get serious
about developing
the time leap machine with me,
to save Kagari
once and for all.
[gasps]
[DARU]
Don't you worry.
I'll do whatever
it takes to finish it,
no matter the cost.
[chuckles softly]
[birds chirping]
[MAHO]
To Japan?
We're lost without
your intelligence.
We need you!
Come help us save the world.
Plus, it would
give me the chance
to see my Mini Maho
in summer clothes, whoo!
Will you wear
a pure white one-piece
and thigh-high socks for me?
--[SUZUHA] Shut up!
--[DARU groans]
[DARU] Sorry,
my overactive imagination
ran away with me again.
But seriously, Maho, come back.
I need to you
to help me figure it out.
'Cause without you, I'll never
restore the Phone Wave.
You really intend
to fix that thing?
[SUZUHA]
I'll say it again.
We need you here, desperately.
[MAHO]
I get it.
Will you at least
let me think this over?
[MAHO] I never pried
into the exact details,
but it's clear.
Makise Kurisu
and Okabe Rintaro
must have gone through
extensive trial and error
in some other world line.
And, somehow,
they successfully
manipulated time.
She was able to do it.
Makise Kurisu
built a time machine.
[ALEXIS]
I can't believe this.
Getting a paper published
at your age is unheard of!
Your talent is the real deal.
And now that the world
has taken notice,
I imagine we're going to get
a lot busier around here!
--[chattering]
--[applause]
[MAHO]
I wanted to crack it.
To prove that I could see
what it held.
I needed to know
that I... could.
[OKABE]
But if you make one wrong move,
you could disgrace that legacy.
You'd be trampling
her memory.
[MAHO]
I'm at a loss.
Should I really
go back to Japan?
[AMADEUS]
Is everything all right, ma'am?
You seem so pensive today.
If you need to talk,
I'd be happy to lend an ear.
That's kind of you.
[gasps]
What's wrong?
[laughs]
[MAHO] Kurisu!
Help me find something!
It's an old magazine!
What? Uh. Sure!
[MAHO]
And also...
[MAHO] I can find the solutions
to this problem myself.
Not by scouring your work
to search out the answers,
but by following
a similar path,
and finding my own
way to success.
[MAHO] And so,
I will go back to Japan.
To the city where my friend,
Makise Kurisu, lost her life.
My exact reasons are hard
to put into words,
but... but I think,
if I had to explain the impetus,
there was one person
who appreciated Mozart's talent
more than anyone else.
And that was Salieri.