And, we're back, with live,
ongoing coverage
of a breaking story:
an alleged terror attack,
right in the heart of our city.
[SAFETY OFFICIAL]
Please proceed...
[REPORTER] Yes, it is a
veritable war zone out here.
As you can see,
the whole front of the station
and Chuo Dori are closed.
[ANCHORMAN] Tell me, are
these attacks still happening
as we speak?
[REPORTER]
That's unclear at the moment,
but sources say
the perpetrators are at large
and possibly planning
for an ambush.
Government officials are
strongly urging citizens
in all 23 wards
to seek shelter
and remain indoors until
the situation is under control.
The Tokyo Disaster
Response Department
continues to urge residents
of all 23--
[sirens wailing]
[MAHO]
This is reality, right?
Not a dream.
It is.
I can't believe it.
They're both dead.
There's still the possibility
they made the jump.
The time machine had already
activated, hadn't it?
[OKABE]
You saw the missiles hit.
We all did.
[OKABE]
Is it true you haven't finished
the time leap machine yet?
[MAHO]
Yeah. That's correct.
[OKABE]
Then we can't just stand here!
Let's get to work,
before it's too late!
[gasps]
[OKABE]
The time leap machine can jump
up to 48 hours into the past.
That would give us
plenty of notice.
--We could save both of them--
--[MAHO] I don't know how!
If I did,
it would be complete.
Makise Kurisu might
have known how,
but I have no idea.
She would have
finished it long ago.
But I've struggled
from square one,
and that's the damn truth!
I understand
what the stakes are,
but I can't do it!
I know you can,
please don't give up!
[DARU]
Enough of your bullshit!
What are you talking about?
Maho has been giving it
all she's got,
especially since
she found out
why Suzuha's been trying
to change the future!
But you're the one
trying to stop us, you!
And now?
Now you're telling us
we shouldn't give up?!
You should've been
supporting us all along!
If you had,
then Mayushii might still--
Suzuha might still be...
[gasping]
Relax!
Let's just take a step back.
We don't have time to be arguing
amongst ourselves like this.
Okabe.
I need to you describe
everything you recall
about Kurisu's process building
the time leap machine.
Tell me the supplies
that she used.
Do you know how she managed
to send the memory data?
I'll have to think about it.
[MAHO] Honestly,
that's the one question
I didn't want
to have to ask.
I wanted to figure it out
on my own.
But now...
We no longer have time
to indulge my pride.
[OKABE]
We hacked into SERN.
You did?
[OKABE]
Yes.
We hacked their systems,
then used the LHC
to create a mini black hole.
We compressed the memory
data to 36 bytes.
[DARU]
For real?
[MAHO] I can see how
that might be possible.
But theory and actuality
are two different things.
Daru has what it takes
to achieve it.
[MAHO]
Think you can?
We'll see,
but they don't call me
"Super Hacker" for nothin'.
Hmm.
The problem is, this microwave
doesn't seem to be
nearly as stable
as the other one.
Forty-two-inch CRT.
It has to be turned on.
That's the only way this
machine is going to work.
But why would a CRT fix--
Because of the electron gun?
That's it.
The solution the three of us
discovered in the end.
[MAHO]
Uh...
Hey, where are you going?
[OKABE] There's something
that I need to verify.
If anything comes up,
call me right away.
I think the signal interference
is gone now, so...
Verify what? Where?
We don't have time to speculate.
And I think we're gonna
need some help.
[BRAUN]
Hey!
What's with all
the noise up there?
I seem to recall you goin' on
about America and Russia before.
Is there somethin' going down?
[OKABE]
It's too late.
We can't stop it
at this point, but still...
I'll make sure the two
of you are safe.
Hey, come back!
Is everything gonna be okay,
Daddy?
Of course, Nae.
Don't worry.
[OKABE panting]
[OKABE]
World War III is upon us.
I never doubted Suzuha.
I knew what she told me
was the truth.
[OKABE] And yet, it felt like
some distant future,
not an impending doom
that would come this quickly.
[OKABE]
But now I understand.
[SOLDIER A]
No dead in the wreckage.
At least, no civilians.
Only soldiers.
--[typing rapidly]
--[beeping]
--Ready?
--A little more.
But don't quote me on that.
So, what are they trying
to do here?
I'm not entirely sure
about that,
but I do know, whatever it is,
they'll need snacks, meow!
All right.
[door closes]
[RUKA]
Okabe?
[FARIS]
Look who it is!
You came to help?
When there's trouble in Akiba,
I don't loaf around.
I always lend a hand!
[FARIS] I assigned Moe-meow
to lookout duty
and told her
to report back to us.
[inaudible]
[MAYURI] But it feels like
something's missing.
Like someone isn't there
who should be.
And it's not as lively or fun.
[DARU]
Shazam!
I just broke in!
You did?
I haven't actually hacked
anything we're after yet,
but at this rate, I'll have
what we need by morning.
I see.
So?
Can you tell me where you went?
[OKABE]
The Radio Building.
Suzuha and Mayuri's bodies
weren't found
among the wreckage.
What do you think that means?
The obvious.
That we can't be certain
our friends are dead,
and there's still hope.
Oh.
Doesn't that make you happy?
[MAHO]
Yeah.
I came to tell you that,
once we hack in successfully,
the time leap machine
will essentially be done.
[OKABE]
That's great.
But look, even if
we complete it,
we won't know
whether it works or not
unless someone tests it.
[OKABE]
Yeah, we ran into the same issue
when Kurisu finished
the other one.
We felt hesitant to use it.
Luckily, it worked exactly
as we theorized.
That's only because
it was the one she made.
Mine might fail.
But you know what you're doing.
Aren't you confident in that?
[MAHO scoffs]
No, not at all.
Why wouldn't you be?
Because I'm nothing like her.
I'm Salieri, she's Mozart.
[OKABE] "So, please convey
this sacred message
to the one whom
I respect the most.
I have always considered myself
to be characteristically
mediocre, unlike yourself.
It was only you,
the one whom I strove
to emulate, above all.
Because I have never had
any shred of doubt,
you are the one,
true Amadeus."
[MAHO]
That was her.
[OKABE]
It was Amadeus' final message.
Remember, the one that
we discovered on @channel?
[MAHO] There's no way
she was referring to me.
[AMADEUS]
Wrong.
I was definitely
talking about you, ma'am.
[OKABE]
Kurisu?
[AMADEUS]
That's right, look down.
You mean you're okay?
[AMADEUS]
Yeah.
The professor froze my data,
but I suppose
that was only temporary.
Before I knew it, I was here.
--Could Daru have--
--What?
Earlier.
When he heard Amadeus'
data was moved,
he started searching for it.
He was doing that while
trying to hack into SERN?
[OKABE] Yeah, that's a walk
in the park for him.
Knowing it would help you
was an added motivator.
[AMADEUS] Wow,
aren't you the popular girl.
Shut up!
[chuckles] You've got this.
I'm confident.
You have no idea what
we're even talking about.
[AMADEUS]
Nevertheless.
Whatever it is, you can do it.
I know better than anyone.
I'm Kurisu's memories, yeah?
Trust me, you can.
[inaudible]
[computer humming]
[helicopter blades whirring]
Is it really you?
Huh? What was that?
[OKABE]
Nothing.
Sorry.
I must've fallen asleep.
[MAHO]
I'm not surprised,
considering you've been
working nonstop
for the last two days.
How's it going?
It's finally complete.
At least, in theory.
Are you really gonna do this?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
Even though you were
adamantly against it?
I made a promise to Kurisu.
That I'd protect
this world line.
Because...
...she sacrificed her life
so that everyone else's
could be spared.
But now I see
that was never true.
You two must have been so close.
I can tell how important
she was to you.
Amadeus means, "loved by God."
[laughs]
The name suits her.
Kurisu is Amadeus.
[OKABE]
Very soon.
I will use the Phone Wave,
real name TBD,
to time leap into the past.
I thank you, my comrades,
for your unstinting devotion,
and your perseverance
in this noble quest.
[OKABE]
Amadeus.
What do you want?
I was napping.
[OKABE] You saved us.
For that, I'm grateful.
Huh?
The post you made.
If we hadn't seen it
online when we did,
we never would have
finished things in time.
[AMADEUS]
What?
But you ended up helping me out,
recovering my data.
--And I'm just a system, anyway.
--That's beside the point.
[OKABE]
Kurisu.
Huh? Yeah? What?
My sincere thanks.
I hope you know you're
a worthy lab member.
[AMADEUS gasps] Enough
already, just get on with it!
[MAHO] What's this?
Are you embarrassed?
[AMADEUS]
No, not in the least!
[OKABE]
I will never give up.
Though I may
fail ten, a hundred,
or a thousand times,
I'll stay the course.
I'll devote my fraught existence
to this pursuit, if I must.
I care not.
I will hold fast.
For Suzuha and Mayuri.
Kagari, too.
[OKABE]
This is it, the first attempt.
[electricity crackling]
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
Where am I?
Did it work?
[OKABE] It's three in the
afternoon on July the 7th.
[OKABE panting]
[OKABE]
This is good.
I should still have
plenty of time!
[door opens]
Whoa, there, champ.
[MAHO]
What's the matter with you?
[OKABE]
Leskinen's computer.
We must hack into it
immediately,
then locate Kurisu
and Hiyajo's Amadeus data
and delete it all,
plus the backups!
No time to explain.
What on Earth are
you talking about?
[OKABE]
It'll snuff out the spark
that ignites World War III!
--Do as I say!
--[BOTH gasp]
[OKABE] Also, we have to
finish the time leap machine.
There's a possibility
we'll require it!
--Hold on!
--Is this what I think it is?
[OKABE]
Yes.
I came from the future,
and I did it using
the time leap machine!
Wait, that means we figured
out how to finish it!
But how? What do we do?
[OKABE]
I told you.
There's no time
to explain anything.
This entire area is about
to become a war zone.
We have to act fast!
Wait, Okarin, how is that
even possible?
[OKABE]
You're about to witness it.
Phone service will
go out for all of Akiba
in a matter of minutes.
So, you two need to use
the wired network
to find out where
Amadeus' data is hidden.
And no matter what happens,
do not go anywhere
near the Radio Building!
Promise me!
The Radio Building? Why not?
[OKABE] Suzuha and Mayuri are
on the way there as we speak.
[gasps]
So, you really are
from the future.
[OKABE]
You and Daru get captured
if you try to make
your way there.
So please just do as I say
and remain in the lab
until I get back here safely!
Is he saying that this
starts World War III?
It seems a bit far-fetched,
and yet...
[OKABE panting]
[OKABE] What was the exact time
that it all began to happen?
When did Suzuha and Mayuri
get to the Radio Building?
I wish I could remember.
[OKABE] It feels just like
it did back then.
Reality becomes more
like a dream,
repeating over and over.
This vague, ominous sensation.
Growing as the moments pass.
Tightening around my throat.
It should be a dream,
but it's not.
I'm experiencing everything
in real time.
I'm living a nightmare,
one whose horrors
are already known to me,
but there's
no respite in that.
Knowing makes it far worse,
and the formless shadow
that stalks me is the guilt--
no, the shame of my
unspeakable transgression.
I can't escape the despair.
I am caught in the vortex,
spiraling downward
into its vast
and crushing blackness.
--[door opens]
--[OKABE] Mayuri!
[MAYURI]
Okarin.
Please stop! Don't do this!
[gun cocks]
If you come any closer,
I will shoot.
[MAYURI]
No, please don't!
[SUZUHA] I'm sorry, but we
don't have time for goodbyes.
Let's go!
[OKABE]
I came here from the future.
Two days from now,
to be precise.
So, trust me.
I've seen what's
going to happen.
In less than an hour,
this place is going to
devolve into a war zone!
--[SUZUHA] Seriously?
--[OKABE] That's right.
Stratfor, an American shadow
intelligence firm,
finds out about
the time machine
and comes barreling in,
their guns ablaze.
And then, the time
machine gets destroyed.
[MAYURI gasps]
No. That can't be true.
[OKABE]
Right now, you're thinking
that if I advance
one more step,
you'll shoot at my left leg,
missing intentionally,
so that it grazes my thigh.
You followed through before
which is how I know.
[SUZUHA] Then we don't have time
to stand around talking!
We've got to get out of here!
If we get delayed,
and they do show up,
we'll miss our chance
to go back.
We have to get in now!
What are you going back to do?
[SUZUHA]
Operation Arclight.
[OKABE gasps]
[SUZUHA] We're going
to August 21st of last year,
the day that you
gave up the fight.
We will convince you to search
for Steins Gate again.
And make sure you understand
what's at stake.
[SUZUHA]
Mayuri gets it,
and that's why she wants
to do this with me.
[OKABE]
Do you really?
[MAYURI]
Yes. So, please, just let us go.
[MAYURI] I'm a lab
member, too, after all.
My Hikoboshi's blinded
by sadness.
And I know just what he
needs to snap out of it.
[MAYURI]
That's why I've decided to go.
And know this,
I love Hououin Kyouma.
But guess what?
I love Okabe Rintaro even more!
More than anything!
Okarin.
[gasping]
Who am I to stop you, then?
[SUZUHA gasps]
You mean it?
[OKABE] Go! If you
don't leave right now,
--you can't make it!
--[gunshot]
[OKABE]
Kagari?
It can't be!
It's too early for her
to be up here!
--[gun cocks]
--[MAYURI gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Come on!
[groans]
[OKABE]
Don't shoot! It's me!
[SUZUHA grunts]
[yelling]
You can't beat her!
[OKABE]
Don't worry, just get in and go!
I won't!
[OKABE]
I'll handle this myself!
Okey-dokey!
[gasps]
I'm counting on you!
Lab member 002!
Shiina Mayuri!
You hold Operation Arclight
in your hands!
Right!
[OKABE]
Come on, go. Hurry!
Please make it!
--[gunfire]
--[machinery stops]
[gasps]
[KAGARI]
I can hear the voice of God,
in my head.
[OKABE]
Who's this?
[gunfire]
[gasping]
[OKABE]
Professor Reyes?
[ALEXIS]
DURPA. Hurry up.
[helicopter blades whirring]
'Kay! Let's get out of here!
[machinery whirring]
Fire, now.
Please make it.
Please make it!
[explosion]
[OKABE gasping]
[OKABE]
Again?
[OKABE whimpers]
[OKABE]
I failed?
[helicopter blades whirring]
[OKABE]
What is this?
Is the destruction of the time
machine a point of convergence?
If that's true,
then no matter
how many times I try,
no matter what I do,
I'll never be able
to prevent it.
--[TV playing]
--[door opens]
You're back!
What happened?
[DARU] Some serious shit's
going down out there.
What about
Suzuha and Mayushii?
[OKABE]
I'll try again.
--I will press on.
--[DARU] Talk to me.
[OKABE]
No matter what!
[MAHO]
You're really gonna leap again?
Yes.
I'm resolute. I won't fail.
Until I save everyone,
I will spend the rest of
my life leaping back.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
And I'm sorry if it means
rushing you to finish this.
It's cool, but when you go back,
tell past me that
future me promised
to keep helping.
[OKABE] I've heard something
very similar before.
From Kurisu, actually.
Yeah, that does sound like her.
[OKABE]
Mayuri. Suzuha.
Kagari.
I refuse to allow it
to end like this.
I will save you.
I'll save everyone I care about!
[groaning]
I will hold fast.
I'll hold fast!
[electricity humming]