Um, that's great.
I'm happy for her.
It must be nice to have
her memories back.
Uh, yeah...
It sure is...
[MAYURI, KAGARI laughing]
[KAGARI]
Mommy...
Hey, um...
The thing is, Kagari...
--No!
--Huh?
Don't just say that.
Add "love."
[MAYURI]
Oh. Kagari, love?
What is it, Mommy?
[MAYURI chuckles awkwardly]
Wanna share a banana with me?
[KAGARI]
Banana?
Ah! How about I feed it to you?
Uh...
Oh, no, that's okay.
I'll do it myself,
I don't mind.
[KAGARI groans]
But when I was little,
it used to make you so happy
when I would feed you
like you were my baby.
[MAYURI]
Uh...
Well, if you really wanna
feed me, then we can pretend.
Yay! Say, "Ah."
[giggles]
--Okarin...
--Yeah?
[KAGARI giggling]
[DARU]
What do you think?
Could this possibly be
a yuri breakthrough?
Even I feel weird.
[RUKA] So, listen--
can I ask a burning question?
--Ah...
--[MAYURI giggles]
I'm confused.
What makes Mayuri
Kagari's mom, again?
Long story.
[KAGARI giggles]
Mommy. I love you.
[KAGARI]
Wow! This is for me?
[MAYURI]
Yup!
I love it!
Thanks so much, Mommy!
I gotta admit.
It's pretty amazing how well
Mayushii is handling this.
[OKABE] I think it's more
that she's just accepting it
in order to avoid hurting
Kagari's feelings.
So, I'm her mother?
But are you sure?
[OKABE]
I'm sure.
[gasps] But she can't be!
I mean, I haven't even had
a baby or anything like that!
Because she's your
adopted daughter.
Kagari came here in a time
machine with Suzuha.
[MAYURI]
From the future? For real?
Yeah, and you saved my life.
Mommy took me in 'cause I didn't
have any living relatives.
I really did that?
But I don't get it,
I don't have any memory of it.
Of course, you wouldn't.
From your perspective, it only
happens in the distant future.
[crying] Mommy!
Oh.
[KAGARI crying]
You noob, if she
weren't skeptical,
then I'd worry
she was crazy instead.
Fair point.
[KAGARI]
Hey, Okarin!
Look what Mommy gave me!
Cool, right?
Ta-da!
--Hey.
--Ah...
[KAGARI]
It's a present from my mommy!
They match! Isn't that neat?
[KAGARI giggles]
Yeah, as you say,
it's quite "neat."
[DARU]
You know what, Kagari?
Your personality's done a 180.
[OKABE] Because her
memories of the future
with Mayuri came back?
[DARU] You're so much more
cheerful and lively now.
You're almost a Genki Girl.
[KAGARI]
What? Do you really think so?
[OKABE] I suppose this must be
Kagari's original personality.
Yeah, I think she's
wonderful now, too!
Not that she wasn't
wonderful before.
Really? I'm glad to hear it!
Hey, wasn't Suzuha just here?
Where'd she go?
[OKABE]
Yes, good question.
[DARU] I think she went down
to the shop a little while back.
Shoot, I forgot!
I had better hurry to work,
too, or I'll be in trouble!
Gotta go, now, Mommy. Bye!
See ya later!
[giggles]
[MAYURI giggles]
[OKABE] Honestly, it seems
like Kagari's only regained
her childhood memories.
Didn't Suzuha mention that
Kagari was about six years old
when Mayushii adopted
her in the future?
[OKABE]
Supposedly so.
Then later, in 2036,
Kagari traveled back in time
to the past with Suzuha.
She was ten at the time.
[DARU] That was all so that
Suzuha could use an IBN 5100
to fix the Y2K problem, right?
So, she swung by 1975,
then hopped back in the
time machine to go to 1998,
but that's when Kagari
got separated from Suzuha
and went missing.
[OKABE] And Kagari doesn't
remember anything else
until 12 years
after that, in 2010.
When she was found
collapsed at the border
of the Chiba Prefecture.
Then, the other day, she was
almost hit by a truck,
and that's what brought back
her childhood memories.
Maybe.
That means she has
a 12-year memory gap
between age 10 and 22.
[OKABE]
Yeah.
Japan is a peaceful
place to live,
but, still, a helpless,
10-year-old girl
would never've been
able to survive
in the streets by herself.
Somebody, somewhere had
to have been helping her
throughout those 12 years.
There's no way around it.
[OKABE] Possibly, but we've got
no information on that.
[DARU] Miss Kiryu is still
investigating things,
but... as of right
now, at least,
there doesn't seem to be
a single clue to be found.
[OKABE] Until Kagari recovers
those memories somehow,
is there really nothing
we can do?
If only we could
uncover something,
even a single little hint,
then we could investigate.
[KAGARI]
Hello?
I'm sorry I'm late.
I lost track of time.
[KAGARI]
Mister Braun? Are you here?
[SUZUHA]
He went out earlier.
[KAGARI]
I see.
I wish I had known
he wasn't here,
I could've spent more
time with my Mommy.
Uh, I'm just kidding,
I would never skip out
on work like that.
That's right.
Suzuha, look at this!
Mommy just gave me
a new smartphone case
that matches my toy.
[SUZUHA]
Oh, yeah? Fascinating.
And that's not all.
Mommy said she would take
me somewhere fun soon.
You should come with us.
Wouldn't it be great
if we all hung out?
No, thanks, I'm good.
You don't want to?
[SUZUHA] I don't have time
to be screwing around.
[KAGARI]
Is that really it?
Or do you just hate me now?
[SUZUHA]
Why would you ever think that?
Because you say mean stuff
like that with a scary face.
This is just the way
my face looks!
And besides,
I am here on a mission!
[KAGARI]
Your face looked a lot nicer
when you were
stuffing it with curry.
[grunts] That is
totally different!
How am I supposed to fight
on an empty stomach, huh?
Right.
Okay, so what's that frown for?
Oh, nothing, this is just
how my face looks.
You can play games with
your mommy all you want.
But leave me out of it.
It must be
so nice to be you.
You've had all
the time you wanted
to play around with your mom and
dad in this era, haven't you?
'Scuse me?
It's true!
You're so lucky!
You've been able to spend
a whole six months
with both of your parents!
And it's not fair
for you to be so mean
about me finally having
fun with my mommy!
How dare you.
You have no idea
what sacrifices I've made
and on your account!
Do you know how much
precious fuel I've wasted
trying to find you?
I'm sorry you had
to do that, but--
[SUZUHA]
You never tried to contact me!
And then you show up
out of nowhere,
having conveniently
forgotten everything!
[KAGARI]
But... not on purpose!
I didn't try to forget,
it just happened.
Besides, you're the one
who abandoned me,
so if all of this is
anyone's fault, it's yours!
[SUZUHA gasps]
If you hadn't just
disappeared on me,
I wouldn't have
been left all alone.
None of the bad stuff
ever would've happened!
Wait, Kagari. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Yes, you do!
We were out walking that day,
and suddenly you were gone.
You ran off and left me alone.
After that, it was just me.
I was so little and helpless.
What the--? Who gave
you two permission
to stand around doing nothing?
If you've got time to lean,
you got time to clean.
Keep slackin' like that and you
can forget about a paycheck.
[OKABE] You mean
Kagari's memory is off?
Yeah, well, that's what
Suzuha seems to believe, anyway.
It's so weird.
She said that the way Kagari
describes certain events
is different from the way
Suzuha remembers
those things going down.
Then again, her memories
are from when she was little,
so she could've just made up
her own version of stuff.
It's possible, but still.
Huh?
Is that Kagari?
[KAGARI]
Oh. Mommy.
Is there something wrong?
It's just, since my
memory came back,
everybody always
looks so upset.
I wonder.
Maybe it would've been better
if I never remembered anything.
Kagari, no.
[BRAUN]
The causes of memory loss?
[OKABE]
Right.
What's more, there's only
part of her memory
that won't come back.
Don't you find that odd?
Yeah, it does seem a little
too coincidental to be nothing.
But, listen, man,
I'm no expert here.
I don't care about that.
Please, just tell me
anything you can think of
that might help.
[BRAUN] Well, I know all
the normal causes.
An accident, for one.
An illness, or stress,
or maybe some other kind
of emotional trauma.
That's about the extent of it.
But if it's not one of those,
isn't it possible a third party
could've screwed with her mind
and caused all of this?
That is what you suspect
actually happened, right?
I know it is.
I have no idea.
But honestly, would it
be too far-fetched
to assume her mind
had been tampered with?
[BRAUN]
Hmm.
Well, if that's the case,
it very well could be possible.
What do you mean?
I'd say it was brainwashing.
Mind control.
[music playing]
[door slams]
[stammers, sighs]
[OKABE]
I'm, uh...
...confused as to why
you're still living here.
[OKABE]
So, that's it?
[MOEKA]
Mmm.
[phone chimes]
Ah, well, well, well.
[OKABE] Are you positive
there's something there?
[MOEKA]
We'll never know for sure,
unless we go scope it out.
What do you say?
[OKABE exhales]
[DARU]
Honestly?
That sounds really out
of character for you.
Yeah. In hindsight,
I probably said way too much.
To be frank, I think I got upset
because I'm envious of her.
You mean of Kagari?
Yeah.
I wish that I could just
forget about my mission
and just live my life while
everyone spoiled me, y'know?
[DARU]
If you wanted to be spoiled,
you should've just said,
'cause Daddy's happy to oblige.
Dummy.
[DARU]
But seriously.
It's simple. If you
regret what you said,
then why don't you
just apologize to her?
I don't know, Dad.
I'm lousy at that stuff.
I never get the timing right.
But maybe, if the moment
presented itself...
[MAYURI] So, anyway,
that's why I'm thinking
that a party
might be best thing!
A party?
[MAYURI] Mm-hmm. You know,
just a little get-together
to celebrate the fact that
Kagari got her memories back.
Oh, I see. Makes sense.
Mm-hmm, but I don't know.
Do you really think that Kagari
would enjoy something like that?
Yeah, it's a perfect idea.
You're planning it, after all,
so I'm sure she'll love it.
Really? Then it's settled.
I'll let everybody know
and start making
all the preparations.
Planning a party's
the best way to stay busy!
[MAYURI giggles]
[phone vibrates]
[music playing]
[KAGARI] You want me to come
tomorrow evening?
[MAYURI]
Mm-hmm. Since it's a Sunday,
do you think you'd be able to
get to the lab at, say, 5:00?
Of course, that shouldn't
be a problem.
And, since it's to
hang out with you,
I'll ask the boss
to let me go early,
and I'll get there
before 5:00!
Oh! [laughs]
Sorry, but you're not
allowed to come early!
Why not?
[MAYURI chuckles]
[MAYURI] Again, I'm sorry,
but that's a secret!
[KAGARI chuckles]
[MAYURI gasps]
Oh, I get it now. A party.
Hey, hold on!
But why would you think that?
Because any time you start
acting suspicious like this,
it always means
you're throwing a party.
So? Is it?
Well, I'm not telling.
You'll have to wait!
[MAYURI chuckles]
But anyway, like I said,
please don't come
to the lab before 5:00!
[KAGARI]
Okay.
Oh, one more thing.
Would it be okay
if I invited Suzuha?
[gasps]
[KAGARI]
Is there...?
Why would you have to ask?
Well, because you and Suzuha
don't seem to be talking
to each other much lately.
[MAYRUI] I won't pretend to know
what happened between you.
But I do know you're both
super special to me,
and I want you to be happy.
I just hope I can help you
sort things out, you know?
Mommy.
--[KAGARI] All right.
--Huh?
I might've been too hard on her.
I know Suzuha's been
through a lot.
So... tomorrow
when I get to the lab,
and she's there, I'll apologize.
Hopefully, we'll be able
to talk through everything
from the beginning.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[FARIS] Meow! Looks like
somebody went all out again!
You know me!
The food and drinks
are all taken care of, too.
They're scheduled to be
delivered here
right before the party starts!
And I made sure that we've got
enough plates and cups.
[door opens]
Hello.
Suzuha! I'm so glad you came!
Uh, yeah, thanks for
sending me the invite.
By the way, where are
all of the others?
Well, Daru is still out shopping
with Yuki and the girls,
but they should
be here any minute.
Okarin has been gone on some
business since this morning,
and I haven't seen him,
but he said he'd be back
in time for the party.
[BRAUN] In that case,
it could be brainwashing.
[OKABE]
You think so?
Look, I don't know much about
the exact methodology
used to create or destroy
specific memories.
But by using drugs, or some
other sort of technique,
they do claim that memories
can be forcibly repressed.
All I'm saying is that it
isn't entirely impossible.
[OKABE] I swear. If there
are people out there
who did something
like that to Kagari...
[YUKI]
Hi, everyone!
Oh, welcome! Hi!
I'm so glad you guys
could make it!
[DARU] Please...
No more shopping, I beg you.
--[DARU groans]
--[YUKI giggles]
Yoo-hoo! We're here!
Party time!
Thanks so much for having me!
[gasps]
Miss Nae! You are welcome
here, Miss Nae!
[NAE] Check it out.
It's Mister Smileybear!
[YUKI]
Smileybear?
Whoa! Slow down!
You're going too fast!
Mountain days are fleeting.
If we don't hurry,
it'll get dark.
Darkness kills.
[OKABE]
Wait. Stop. No, don't!
[screams]
Can you please not drive like
you're trying to kill us both?!
It's all right. The quicker we
can get there, the better.
[OKABE]
No!
[KAGARI humming]
[gasps]
[humming]
This way.
[OKABE panting]
How can you be so certain
it's back here?
[OKABE]
So it is.
[gasps]
Perfect!
Overall impression?
Recently abandoned.
What? This place has clearly
been vacant for years!
Wrong.
The glass on the ground.
It's relatively fresh.
It was placed there to fool you,
and, apparently, it worked.
My guess?
It's been empty six months,
at most, a year.
Well?
Shall we keep looking, then?
Let's go.
[WOMAN]
Thanks so much, come again.
[KAGARI]
It's still a little early.
But that's okay.
[giggles]
[KAGARI]
I hope Suzuha does come.
I really wanna clear the air.
[music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[MAYURI]
Just to be sure I understand.
You're saying Kagari
still needs treatment?
[DOCTOR] Yes, she might appear
to be healed on the surface,
but in order to
completely treat the PTSD
brought about by the war,
it's going to take a
significant amount of time.
[KAGARI] But I don't like
the treatment, Mommy.
It gives me bad headaches
that won't go away.
Think you can tough it out
just a little longer?
Mommy will be
right there with you.
'Kay?
[KAGARI]
I'll do it.
[DOCTOR]
Come on, then, Kagari.
Let's make our best effort
today, all right?
[gasping]
I hear it. That sound.
It is the voice of God
calling to me.
[FARIS]
Kaga-meow is really late.
[RUKA]
But she promised.
She said she would come
straight here at 5:00.
I wonder if something
held her up.
[MAYURI] I'm sure it's nothing.
I'll call her again.
'Kay.
Well, I'm going out
to look for her.
Suzuha?
[clanging]
[MOEKA]
I found something.
What is it? You hear
a strange noise?
I saw a switch on the wall.
I pressed it and opened this.
Do you see?
[OKABE]
A hidden passage?
[MOEKA]
Okabe, look.
In here.
[OKABE gasps]
What... is this place?
Does this mean that Kagari
was kept locked up in here?
[OKABE]
By whom?
What kind of monster
would do such a thing?
And why?
[rain falling]
[phone vibrating]
This is Okabe.
[MAYURI] Ah! Okarin!
Thank goodness you picked up!
[OKABE]
Mayuri, what's wrong?
It's Kagari,
she never showed up!
We can't find her anywhere!
[OKABE]
She's gone missing?