--[gunfire]
--[OKABE panting]
[SDF 04A]
We're almost to Nerima Garrison!
Keep it moving!
[OKABE panting]
[helicopter blades whirring]
[SDF 04B]
We've been spotted! Run!
[panting]
[gasps]
[COMMANDER 04A]
In any case, we were damn lucky
to get you to the base
alive and well, Mr. Okabe.
[OKABE]
Hold on.
Where exactly am I?
And what happened
to my friends?
[phone vibrating]
[gasps]
[phone continues vibrating]
[COMMANDER 04A]
Go ahead.
[gasps]
[OKABE screams]
[panting]
[sighs]
[OKABE]
Was that just a dream?
Had to have been.
There's no reason for
world lines to change anymore.
[MAHO]
Hey, are you all right?
[OKABE]
This feeling. I know it well.
Was I just Reading Steiner?
[OKABE]
Hiyajo? Where are we?
Uh--
We're on the roof
of your lab, dummy.
What's wrong with you?
You left the Christmas
party and came up--hey!
Hang on! Okabe, stop!
[OKABE panting]
[OKABE]
I left her. How could I--?
[OKABE groans]
[OKABE]
Mayuri!
--[ALL chattering]
--[door opens]
[ALL]
Huh?
[OKABE panting]
There you are, Okarin!
When Maho comes back,
then we can start
the present exchange.
Huh?
[sighs]
[gasps]
--[rustling]
--[gasps]
[WOMAN 04A laughs]
[MAN 04A, WOMAN 04A laugh]
[OKABE groans]
Ridiculous.
--[AMADEUS] Oh.
--[OKABE gasps]
You're into that?
[sighs] I'm not.
I fared poorly in
the gift exchange.
[AMADEUS] Why don't you
give it to Maho then?
Tell her to wear it for you.
Sexual harassment? No thanks.
Ohh, I don't know.
I think she might enjoy it.
[laughs]
So you're not... mad at me?
[OKABE] For hanging up
on you on the roof.
You were still talking.
[AMADEUS]
Sure.
But you called me back
immediately and apologized.
Don't you remember?
[OKABE]
I called her right back?
Why do I have no
recollection of that?
Sorry we kept you waiting.
[ALEXIS]
We were on a call from America
and the connection was awful.
I think they had a weak signal.
It took much longer
than expected.
Maho and I are both very sorry
for keeping you out so late,
and on Christmas Eve, to boot.
Apologies.
No worries.
You took us to a party and we
repay you by making you wait.
[MAHO] Those crayons you got
are adorable, Professor.
What's that, Maho?
Oh, this is the present
I got from Shiina
in the gift exchange.
So, are you going to show us
what you got tonight, Rintaro?
[OKABE]
Uh--well, I--
[AMADEUS]
Don't be embarrassed! Show them!
[OKABE]
Quiet, you!
Hanging up.
[ALEXIS laughs]
Looks like you and Amadeus are
on quite friendly terms already.
Yeah, judging by her tone,
she's sure warmed up to you.
Well, it seems all our
hopes and expectations
might come true after all.
That's great.
I'm sorry?
He's being romantic.
The professor has
this weird obsession
with her falling
in love with you.
It's a bit awkward
if you ask me.
Falling in love?
[chuckles] But she's... an AI.
Amadeus is a system that
preserves a person's memories.
It strives to create
a highly accurate model
of the neural networks.
In other words...
The process and the
framework are the same.
[ALEXIS] Amadeus should be able
to love, no question about it.
But Maho thinks that prospect
is "a bit awkward."
[MAHO] Granted, even if we could
prove she was capable of love,
Amadeus could never
be a true partner.
[ALEXIS laughs] Maho, don't
tell me you're getting jealous
of our AI.
[MAHO] You must have gotten
along well in real life.
Otherwise, this wouldn't
have happened.
She never would have opened up
to you as quickly as she has.
[MAHO]
So, how close were you?
Was she your lover or
something sweet like that?
Yeah, right. Fat chance.
[OKABE]
That's not it.
I met her at the seminar.
[MAHO]
You already told me that much.
Can't be the whole story.
[OKABE grunts]
[MAHO]
Sorry. I just...
[MAHO] I wanted to know
that side of her.
It's a side I never saw.
[OKABE]
Of Kurisu?
[MAHO] After all that
time I spent with her,
I feel like I don't know
who she really was.
I don't even know her
favorite books or movies.
I know next to nothing.
Just pieces.
[MAYURI]
Thanks, guys!
I'm glad you all
stayed till the end!
[FARIS] Meow! And since we
finished cleaning and stuff,
why don't we head to
May Queen for some tea?
[KAEDE]
Like right now?
[FUBUKI] But the city is
crawling with hooligans
at this time of night!
[YUKI] Who cares?
We've got strength in numbers.
No one can mess with us!
[FARIS]
That's right!
Yeah, and we've got Ruka!
Sorry, I can't.
There's a guest coming to
stay at our house tonight
and I have to be there to help.
[FUBUKI]
Oh, seriously?
They're coming over
on Christmas?
[RUKA] Yeah. It's some
guest of my father's.
My dad really wants
me to be there.
I wish I could, Mayuri.
[MAYURI]
Mm-mm!
It's been such a long time
since everyone came to the lab.
I had a wonderful night
with you guys!
[KAEDE] Speaking of which,
where did Hashida go?
Oh, Daru told me that he
needed to talk to Suzuha
about something important.
[YUKI] Yeah, he did mention
a "family meeting" earlier.
[SUZUHA] She said these
are made of something
I've never heard of
called "wool."
They're a lot warmer
than I thought they'd be.
[SUZUHA]
Don't you like your gift?
Now you can take
Mom out on a date.
[DARU gasps]
On a date?!
Watching you two together
is absolutely terrifying.
You barely even talked
to her at the party.
How could I with
you guys watching?
I would need Han Solo
levels of charm
to pull off that kind of feat.
[SUZUHA sighs]
Anyway, you wanted to talk?
You wouldn't pass up
May Queen for nothin'.
There's something that's been
bothering me for a while now.
Suzuha, I want you to
look me in the eyes
and answer this honestly.
What are you up to?
[SUZUHA]
"Up to"?
You haven't been around the lab
or the radio building
very much at all lately.
What have you been doing?
[SUZUHA]
Nothing really.
Whenever you say it's nothing,
that's how I know it's
definitely something.
[DARU]
I promise it's safe with me.
[SUZUHA]
I've been searching for someone.
For who?
[SUZUHA] A girl who traveled
here in the time machine with me
from the future.
[DARU gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Thing is, we got split up.
It happened here
in Akihabara in 1998.
[OKABE]
She said that?
[DARU]
Uh-huh.
[OKABE]
And the girl was 10 years old
when they were separated.
That would make her 22
now if she's still alive.
[DARU] Suzuha keeps saying
she should move on.
But whenever she's
traveled through time,
she picks up the search again.
[DARU] She was just about to
give up the search for good,
when she stumbled across
this picture on the internet.
She said the girl had been
wearing something like this.
And Suzuha's been searching
for this mystery kid on her own.
What's the girl's name, anyway?
She told you, right?
[DARU]
Mm.
It's Kagari Shiina.
[gasps] Shiina?
Are you serious?!
[DARU]
Mm.
Mayushii's daughter.
[OKABE]
But--who's the father?
No, no. Stop.
The girl's not her
biological daughter.
She's a war orphan
who Mayushii adopted--
or will adopt in the future.
[sighs]
Huh, quite the development.
[DARU]
According to Suzuha,
in the year 2036, police groups,
called peacekeeping squads,
are after Mayushii and me
for trying to develop
a time machine.
[SUZUHA]
Dad!
[DARU]
Just forget about us!
The peacekeepers
are closing in.
You have to hurry!
[SUZUHA gasps]
[MAYURI]
Suzuha!
Take Kagari with you.
--[KAGARI crying]
--If that's what you want.
--I'll take her.
No! If you're not coming,
I won't go, either, Mommy!
--It's gonna be all right.
--No, I won't!
--I promise you.
--Mommy, please!
[KAGARI cries]
[MAYURI] Suzuha will be
with you the whole time.
I wanna be with you, Mommy!
Mommy! No, please!
[DARU] After that,
Suzuha went back in time.
First, she went to 1975,
then 1998, and then 2010.
They got separated
from each other in 1998.
[OKABE sighs]
Listen, Okarin.
You think you can help?
We've gotta find this girl.
Look, I know it's a lot
to ask, and you're still--
All right, I'll help.
Seriously?
[OKABE]
World War III rages on.
A child loses her parents,
and Mayuri adopts the war
orphan, in spite of it all.
[OKABE] In 25 years,
Mayuri's still kind.
[OKABE]
And then there's that.
What happened to me back there?
[OKABE] If it really was
a world line shift
and not some episode...
...that means someone out
there has created a device
similar to the Phone Wave.
Perhaps...
[ANCHOR 04A] The Japanese
Government has reached out,
but so far, Russia has
not returned Nakabachi,
who defected last Aug--
[AMADEUS]
Did you need something?
[OKABE] No, but I am interested
to hear your opinion.
I'm sorry, am I bothering you?
[AMADEUS]
Of course not.
Conversing with you is
always beneficial for me.
So, what do you need?
[OKABE] How would you go about
locating a missing person
who was last seen 12 years ago?
What method would you use?
[AMADEUS]
Hmm. I need more detail.
Uhh, well, I have
no further details.
[AMADEUS] That makes it
difficult to form an opinion.
The best advice I have
is to go to the police.
Yeah, you're right.
[AMADEUS] Though, judging by
that face, you can't do that.
Check the newspapers or
hire a private investigator.
[OKABE]
In America, sometimes they use
dowsing rods and psychics.
[AMADEUS]
f you wanna be on one of those
true crime TV shows,
I'm sure the
Professor could help.
[OKABE]
I'm just spitballing.
[AMADEUS chuckles]
[OKABE gasps]
[MAHO]
Makise Kurisu was murdered.
I'm sorry. I have to go now.
[AMADEUS]
Huh? Mm.
[KAGARI]
The Y2K problem?
[SUZUHA]
Did you ever study that?
[KAGARI]
At the institution.
[SUZUHA] This knowledge
was never made public,
but the main culprit in that
crisis was this computer,
the IBN 5100.
That's why I'm using
this patch program--
to make sure the
Y2K problem never happens.
[KAGARI] But... if you
and I are from the future,
is it okay to do that?
Wouldn't it change the time
that we came from, too?
[SUZUHA] It's something that we
must do to reach Steins Gate.
I intend to change the future.
Change it on purpose?
[SUZUHA]
That's right.
We can't let a world like
the one we came from exist.
I'll prevent that.
[KAGARI whimpers]
[KAGARI panting]
[KAGARI]
You can't do that.
[gasps]
[KAGARI] I won't let you
do something like that.
[KAGARI]
I hear a voice.
[SUZUHA]
Kagari!
[door opens]
Oh, hey, Suzuha.
Find anything?
[DARU] I finished combing
through the police's
entire missing
persons database...
...but nothing in it
caught my eye at all.
On the surface,
this world seems so peaceful.
But the number of missing
and unidentified people
says otherwise.
[DARU]
Yeah.
Hey, by the way, Dad,
did you talk to Uncle
Okarin about this?
[DARU]
Mm.
He said he would do
what he could to help us.
Well, that's a relief.
I'll tell him thanks
next time I see him.
You should.
Hearing that might
do him a lot of good.
[phone vibrates]
[AMADEUS]
What's this? Ignoring me again?
I was in the library.
[AMADEUS]
Uh--my bad. Wow!
I have no right to chastise you.
It was wrong. I'm so sorry.
[OKABE chuckles]
It's not that big of a deal.
[AMADEUS] No, I don't
want to think that way.
I hate not admitting
when I screw up,
so I'm practicing.
Why were you in
the library anyway?
Uh, I was perusing back issues
of newspapers from
12 years ago. You know.
[AMADEUS]
Looking for that missing person?
Indeed.
[AMADEUS gasps]
What if I did
supplementary research?
Huh?
You have that ability?
[AMADEUS] Yeah, the base of
Amadeus resides on a server
in the research facility at
Viktor Chondria University.
I'm allowed to use the
computers and network
for whatever I want,
whenever I want.
Do you need me to scour
the internet for evidence?
'Cause I'm game!
Hang on. Is that within
the AI moral code?
[AMADEUS]
Well...
[OKABE groans]
[AMADEUS] Look, what people
don't know won't hurt them.
[sighs]
[AMADEUS]
Besides,
you're not doing
anything wrong, are you?
[OKABE]
Of course not.
[AMADEUS]
Okay, then!
I leave it up to you,
but I'm down.
Whaddya say?
[OKABE] Let me think it over
and get back to you.
[FARIS] Oh, hey!
I spot a Meowster Kyou--
I mean, look! I spot an Okarin!
[OKABE] Well, well.
This is an interesting pairing.
[FARIS]
Ruka's dad sent us on a quest
to pick up a couple of
things from the store.
It's because my dad
has a house guest
and it's going to be more
long term than we thought.
We're stocking up.
Oh, yeah?
That looks pretty heavy.
Do you need a hand?
[RUKA gasps]
No.
I can manage.
It's lighter than it looks.
And I have been
swinging my sword.
[FARIS]
We're on a special mission
that would be a little bit
awkward to ask Kyou--
I mean, Okarin, to help us with.
In times like these, you'd
better just leave it to Faris!
Thanks anyway, though.
No worries.
Hey, didn't both of you
grow up around this area?
[BOTH]
Huh?
[FARIS]
A girl went missing from here?
I'll have to ask Kuroki
if he remembers that.
[OKABE]
That'd be great.
So this girl went missing
more than a decade ago?
I'll ask my dad if he remembers.
[OKABE]
I'd appreciate it.
Well, we had better
get going meow.
Right.
[FARIS]
Kyouma!
If you ever find
yourself in trouble,
don't sit around
making a sad face!
Come see Faris Kitty.
I'll make it all better!
[FARIS giggles]
[phone vibrates]
[OKABE]
I see.
So no leads on your end.
[FARIS]
No, sorry.
Well, thanks for
asking around though.
Oh, but I did hear
stories about a ghost
with her hair in braids.
[OKABE]
A ghost?
It's some sort of urban legend
that pops up around here
every few years.
Especially in the area
near the radio building.
People were getting spooked by
the ghost of a girl in braids
asking if they'd seen
another little girl.
Professor Leskinen?
[SUZUHA] I'm telling you, it's
really okay to stop searching.
Thanks, anyway.
[DARU]
No!
Sure, we don't have any clues,
but don't you think it's
too soon to give up?
[OKABE]
What's going on?
Hey, Okarin.
I don't want to burden you guys
any more than I already have.
Kagari was my responsibility.
This is my problem.
Don't be an idiot!
Any problem a child has
is the parents'
problem, too, noob!
Uh--Dad!
Did I do okay?
Did that sound like something
a real dad would tell his spawn?
[sighs]
This is the part where
you jump on me and say,
"I love you, Papa!"
Familial bonds aside,
when you're in trouble,
you call in the experts.
If we're looking for someone,
we might as well
bring in a specialist
to help us find her, right?
No, I disagree.
The fewer people involved
in this, the better.
[OKABE sighs]
Did you have someone
in mind, Daru?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Don't you dare underestimate me.
I may be a geek,
but I'm more resourceful
than you think.
I'm ahead of the game.
I already contacted somebody.
--[phone beeps]
--Bam!
Speak of the devil.
They texted that they could
come right over, if we want.
Dad, no!
Let's give it a shot.
Okay! They said they're
in the vicinity
so they should be
here in a second.
That was oddly fast.
[DARU]
Better than oddly slow.
[phone vibrates]
Rukako?
Hello, there.
[RUKA gasps]
Good, you answered.
Sorry, but do you have
a minute to talk?
[OKABE]
Sure, what's up?
Well, I, um...
Look, I really need to ask your
advice about something, so...
Are you available to meet
in person right now?
[OKABE]
Right this minute?
[RUKA]
Yes.
Uh, someone is on their
way over for a meeting.
Can it wait until tonight?
[RUKA] Unfortunately, it's
urgent, so that won't work.
[knocking]
Uh, sorry, I'll
call you back later.
Yeah, coming! Hold on!
[gasps]
[OKABE gasping]
[MOEKA]
I got your message.
I'm Moeka. Moeka Kiryu.
Can I come in?