[footsteps]
[SUZUHA]
So this is where you've been.
I should have guessed.
[MAYURI]
Oh, Suzu.
Dad and the others
are looking for you.
They said they're about
to kick off the operation.
Mayu?
[MAYURI]
What if...
What if I'd acted differently?
[MAYURI] If I'd just done
things another way...
...and reached my hand out?
Would this future be different?
[MAYURI]
That day...
...if my Hikoboshi had
burned bright just once more,
it might have changed
everything for us.
[MAYURI]
What if when he fell...
...I'd reached out
and touched him?
[MAN 01A]
You are drifting down.
Plunging through your memories.
As you sink ever deeper,
you see a light.
It entrances you.
Tell me, what color
is the light?
It's red.
[MAN 01A] Standing within
this brilliant aura
is someone of great
importance to you.
Is it a family member?
She's not.
Then a friend, perhaps.
Or maybe a lover?
[OKABE]
She doesn't even know me.
She and I... We haven't...
[MAYURI gasps]
[MAYURI]
Okarin!
Uh--
[MAYURI giggles]
[OKABE]
Hey, what gives?
I told you there was no reason
to wait around for me.
[MAYURI chuckles]
How was your session?
Good.
Turns out hypnotherapy
works well
for someone with a
robust temporal lobe.
The doc says I'll be fine.
Wow! You mean it?
Yeah, but he does want me
to keep up the counseling
for a while.
You were right about it helping.
I'm glad I took your advice.
[MAYURI]
That's such a relief.
Honestly, it seemed
like you were
having a pretty
rough time lately.
I'm sorry if I worried you.
[MAYURI]
Mm-mm.
How 'bout we go
grab a bite to eat?
It's my treat.
In that case, why don't
we head over to Akiba
for old time's sake?
[OKABE]
Huh?
[MAYURI] Ruka and Faris invited
me out a little while ago
and it sounded like fun.
Akihabara, huh?
Can we?
[OKABE]
Sure. Of course.
[MAYURI]
That's the best news!
I'll tell everyone we're
on our way. One sec!
Hey, Faris!
Guess what! Guess what!
[OKABE]
It's cold.
Somehow, December already.
[OKABE]
And yet...
...it feels like the summer
happened moments ago.
[door chimes]
Let's see.
They said they'd be waiting
in here for us somewhere, so...
[MAYURI gasps]
[MAYURI]
Ruka! Faris! We're here!
Too-too-roo!
I'm glad you could
make it, Mayuri.
Kyouma!
[OKABE]
Rukako. Faris.
Been a while since
I've seen you.
We're well aware.
[FARIS] Kyouma! I missed
you so much, meow!
[OKABE] Hey! Will you
cut this nonsense out?
[FARIS]
What for, meow?
Kyouma knows he likes it, meow.
[OKABE]
All right. More importantly,
will you please stop
calling me that?
Meow come?
Because it's from the dark past.
[FARIS grunts] Just tell me who
I have to paw to get it back!
These claws'll show 'em
not to mess with my Kyouma.
--Of course.
--[RUKA] You know,
this kinda feels
like the old days.
I go to the lab
every now and then,
but I never see you
there anymore, Okabe.
[OKABE]
Well, I've been quite busy.
Don't tell me!
You've been captured
by a secret society?
Unfortunately, I'm just swamped
with college seminars.
But there are clubs as well.
Meow! Meow!
You actually joined a club?
Do you guys research UFOs
and Bigfoots and stuff?
No. I'm now a tennis star!
--[RUKA] Are you serious?
--[FARIS] What?!
[MAYURI chuckles]
One of my professors
is the advisor.
You'd be shocked
at my proficiency.
I never really pegged
you as a sportsman.
[MAYURI] Look out, Wimbledon!
Here comes Okarin.
[RUKA]
So practicing day and night
must be why you're
so busy, right?
Well, uh, it's not
really that intensive.
Then what have you
been doing without us?
[OKABE] Well, if you must know,
I've had some, uh, group dates.
--[FARIS] Group?
--[RUKA] Dates!
--[FARIS screams]
--[RUKA] What?!
Dates with multiple girls?
What perverted group
are you running in?
And you think it's okay
to flaunt your love life
in front of us?
--College has changed you.
--You disgust me, meowster.
Why are you ganging up on me?
I'm just partaking in
normal student affairs.
[FARIS]
You are so gross!
--[MAYURI chuckles]
--I expected better!
Explain yourself, Kyouma.
[RUKA]
How could you, Okabe?
[MAYURI gasps]
A message from Yuki!
[ALL gasp]
[FARIS]
What? Is something wrong?
[MAYURI]
Mm-mm.
She wants to know if
I'm around Akiba now
because she has something
she really wants to show me.
At the lab.
[OKABE gasps]
[MAYURI gasps]
[OKABE]
In that case...
...let's go!
[DARU]
Why you dirty...
This calls for all-out war!
Leave no comment left untrolled!
"Normals Must Die-P"
was never one of us!
He's nothing but a damned liar!
How could you marry
Parthenon, you fraud?!
[SUZUHA]
Cool it, Dad.
[DARU] Whoa! @channel
and Twipo are on fire.
--[SUZUHA groans]
--I bet those two get doxxed!
I can't believe I didn't
know about this sooner!
This is why you never
step away from--
[gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Listen to me if you wanna live.
[DARU whimpers]
[DARU] Suzuha, put that down
or Daddy will get angry!
[SUZUHA] I'm already
plenty mad for both of us!
[DARU sighs]
Right. Sorry.
[SUZUHA]
Get it together!
All you ever do
around here is nap,
play games, and mess
around on the internet!
[DARU]
Not my fault every time I start
working on time
machines, I crash.
Plus, we've already got one.
You could just use
that as my template.
[SUZUHA]
No, I can't,
because it's the one you
invented in the future!
If you saw it now,
you'd run the risk
of creating a time paradox
and all kinds of problems.
Well, if it's guaranteed
that I make the thing,
then who cares?
I'll get right on it! Tomorrow!
[SUZUHA]
I am telling you,
it is time you started
working on it seriously.
[sighs] I remember Mom
used to get on your back
for procrastinating like this.
[DARU]
I'd welcome her on my back.
Know what I mean? [chuckles]
That's so gross!
[DARU]
Yeah, forget that.
[SUZUHA]
In the future,
you always say
that this world line
is the worst one imaginable.
But having me
was the best thing
that ever happened
to the two of you.
I came here to convince
Uncle Okarin that somehow
we could figure out a way
to change the future.
But since that day,
he hasn't been back to the
lab and nothing is different.
[SUZUHA gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Someone's here.
[footsteps]
Uh, what are the
chances it's Okarin?
It's not! I hear
boots. It's Mom!
[gasps]
[DARU]
You gotta hide!
I am so on it!
--[knocking]
--[DARU gasping]
--[DARU] Yeah? Come in.
--[door opens]
Hello, hello! How was your day?
[DARU]
Ah. Amane, hey!
What brings you to the lab?
[YUKI giggles]
[YUKI]
Oh, dear. Mayuri isn't here?
Mayushii? No,
I haven't seen her.
Oopsie! I think I must be early.
She said she was
gonna meet me here
with some of the other girls.
[DARU]
That so?
Do you mind if I wait
in here with you?
[DARU]
Uh, no, sure!
Perfect. Thank you!
Um, is your little sister
out and about in town today?
Huh? Little sister?
What do you mean?
I'm sorry. Your little sister.
Um, well, all of my little
sisters are strictly 2D.
Uh--oh, yeah! You were
talking about Suzuha!
[YUKI] Of course.
Who else would it be?
Uh...
--[sighs]
--Well... nobody?
[door opens]
Too-too-roo!
[DARU gasps]
Oh, there you are!
Too-too-roo, to you,
Yuki! [giggles]
[FARIS]
Meow, meow!
Yay! Faris and Ruka came, too!
[DARU]
Faris, my feline fantasy!
[gasps]
[OKABE]
What do ya know?
Nothing's changed.
[DARU]
Okarin!
Mind if I come in?
Hallucinations and
memory problems
prompting the
Ministry of Health to...
You don't have to ask
me for permission.
It's your lab, isn't it?
I suppose so.
[MAYURI gasps]
Wow, Yuki, your clothes
are so cute!
I knew that's what
you were going to say!
That's why I wanted
to show you.
[FARIS whines] Do a catwalk
twirl for me, please!
[DARU] We've got some sodas
here if you're thirsty.
Wait, Okarin!
Where are you going?
What? Can't a man use
his lab's bathroom?
--[DARU sputters]
--[SUZUHA gasps]
[DARU grunts, clears throat]
The toilet's been
acting kinda weird!
[OKABE]
Uh...
[DARU groans, sighs]
[OKABE sighs]
[creaking]
Uh--
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp, groan]
[thud]
--[MAYURI gasps]
--Kyouma?
[RUKA]
Are you okay?
[OKABE, SUZUHA groaning]
[SUZUHA gasps]
Oh, hi, Suzu.
Um, hey, there! [chuckles]
[BOTH]
Ta-da!
[YUKI giggles]
So pretty!
[FARIS]
Meow!
[DARU]
It's a feast for my eyes
and I'm about to
order seconds, girl!
[YUKI giggles]
Hey, where did Okarin go?
He went up to the roof
with Suzuha earlier.
Seemed like they wanted to
talk about something important.
Oh, okay.
[OKABE] You didn't have
to come up with a lie
in the first place, you know.
Saying you're his little
sister complicates things.
Makes you more suspicious.
[SUZUHA] I get that,
but how was I supposed to know
that Mom would wanna
hang out with me so much?
[OKABE] We should've had a plan
before Daru and Yuki met.
[SUZUHA]
That day at Summer ComiMa.
Who knew she'd be one of
Mayu's cosplay friends
before she'd ever met Dad?
--[thud]
--[YUKI, DARU gasp]
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Huh?
Huh?
[SUZUHA]
And suddenly, there she was.
[sputtering]
[OKABE] She has no idea that one
day she'll give birth to you.
I wonder if she
feels a connection
even if she can't
quite place it.
[SUZUHA] Dad said he'll explain
everything sooner or later.
When the time's right.
[OKABE]
Hm.
Still though,
it's hard to believe they'll
have a kid together.
Well, get used to it,
because the fact
that I'm still here
means the future
hasn't changed at all.
[jet engine roaring]
[SUZUHA gasps]
[sighs]
[SUZUHA]
This world's so peaceful.
No one knows to be scared.
By the time I was grown up,
you'd only see scenes like
these in photos and old movies.
[OKABE] World War III
ravages everything.
[SUZUHA] Yeah, and because
Dad and the others
were building a time machine,
we were seen as
a rebel organization.
[OKABE]
At least you and your parents
managed to escape alive somehow.
[SUZUHA]
No, my Mom was mowed down
in a barrage of bullets
trying to protect me
--[OKABE gasps]
--from a military drone.
[sighs]
I saw her body ripped to
shreds right before my eyes.
I was practically
showered in her blood.
Uncle Okarin?
The future in store for this
world line is a living hell.
[SUZUHA] So many countries start
fighting over time machines
that the death toll
is unfathomable.
There are decades of
horror and despair ahead!
We're talking about the lives
of billions of people here!
You can change it!
[OKABE gasping]
I am begging you.
Please. Please...
[OKABE]
I can't.
[gasps] Uncle!
[OKABE] I've drifted through
so many different world lines
that I've lost count.
[SUZUHA gasps]
[OKABE]
The one constant is that
no matter what
reality I step into,
time machines destroy lives.
I've seen them drive you
to ruin, too, damn it!
Over and over.
Loops of misery.
Believe me, I know how useless
someone can be against time!
[OKABE]
No matter what I tried...
...I was powerless.
You say that, but you have
altered world lines before.
You told me that yourself.
So then... why not?
[OKABE]
It won't work!
You can't just change the
past to switch world lines!
It breaks the fundamental rules
that govern our universe.
Humans like us were never meant
to tamper with such powers.
The moment we start
meddling, we're punished!
It's too much!
I'd rather tear my eyes out
than see it all again!
Only you can do it.
[OKABE panting]
[SUZUHA]
We still have some time.
Please give it another
thought, for me!
This isn't over.
--[door opens]
--I haven't given up.
[door slams]
[MAYURI] I guess Suzu had other
stuff she needed to do, huh?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
The two of you didn't fight
up there on the roof, did you?
[OKABE]
That's not what happened.
[MAYURI]
I see.
Ooh! I didn't think it was
gonna be this chilly today.
[MAYURI] At least the lab
was lively for a change.
It was a lot of fun
seeing everyone.
Is that right?
Yep!
To be honest with you,
for some reason,
I've felt really lonely
every time I've gone
over there lately.
It's been sad.
[OKABE]
Even though Daru's there?
[MAYURI]
Yeah.
And it's strange,
because before,
I used to wait in the lab
all by myself for you,
so I should be used to that.
There's no reason for me
to feel alone when I'm there.
But it's just...
Sometimes it's so overwhelming
that it makes me want to cry.
--[OKABE gasps]
--Big ugly tears, you know?
Kind of feels like
there used to be
a bunch more people
hanging around.
[OKABE]
It's an illusion.
Huh?
[OKABE]
Just a dream.
There were only three people
that ever came to the lab.
You and me, and Daru
at the computer.
[MAYURI]
Hmm, I guess you're right.
[phone vibrates]
[MAYURI]
Is it a bad message?
[OKABE] No. Some people from
Viktor Chondria University
are giving a seminar
in Akiba tomorrow.
I was hoping to talk with
one of their professors,
but I guess they've gone
out drinking for the night.
[MAYURI gasps]
So weird!
It's like you're
totally normal now.
I'll be perfectly
fine by myself.
Go meet them!
[OKABE]
Okay.
Sorry for ditching you.
[chattering]
[OKABE] Artificial
Intelligence Revolution.
Viktor Chondria University.
Professor Alexis Leskinen.
[OKABE]
It's... the college she went to.
[MAKISE]
I'm so scared.
I think I'm dying.
But... I don't want to die!
[OKABE gasping]
[OKABE screaming]
[gagging]
[OKABE panting]
[MAHO]
Hey. Excuse me.
You work here, right?
[OKABE]
Uh--huh?
Which way do I go to
get to the staff room?
Uh...
--[MAHO] Hmm?
--[OKABE] Uh...
Oh, you must be lost.
This is a university-level
conference.
I'm well aware, you idiot!
[OKABE stammers]
[MAHO sighs]
It's the same thing every time.
[OKABE]
What do you mean?
You're the fourth
person to tell me
I'm in the wrong place
since I arrived here.
"Viktor Chondria University."
Part of the Brain
Science Institute.
Oh, I get it. You're
returning someone's--
Ugh! Fourth time for that, too!
[MAHO grunts]
[OKABE] Wait, you're telling me
the school is letting in...
...middle schoolers?
[MAHO]
Now you're just being insulting!
There's no university that
accepts people that young!
[OKABE]
You're 21 years old?
[MAHO] In other words,
I'm a full-grown woman!
Not in middle school,
elementary school, or preschool!
You got that?
But--sure.
[OKABE]
I was in the wrong.
[gasps]
[OKABE]
I'm sorry.
[MAHO scoffs]
Yeah, okay, whatever.
It's always like this,
no matter what country I go to.
[OKABE]
Shocking.
What was that?
[OKABE]
Uh, nothing! Just a cough.
[sighs]
[OKABE]
Uh, wrong direction.
You want the staff room?
Go out that way,
and then it's the door
at the end of the hall.
Thanks for the help.
[OKABE]
Twenty-one, huh?
I can practically
hear Daru shouting,
"Legal loli for the win!"
[gasps]
[OKABE]
That's... Kiryuu Moeka!
Why...?
What is she doing here?
[OKABE]
No. Not again!
Calm down.
This is the beta world line.
It's nothing like the other one.
[OKABE]
It can't be.
[applause]
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
It's...
...that girl.
Good day, everyone.
[MAHO speaking Japanese]
[ALEXIS] Thank you for
attending my seminar.
I am Alexis Leskinen from
Viktor Chondria University's
Brain Science Institute.
This is my interpreter
and assistant, Hiyajo Maho.
[speaking Japanese]
[applause]
The topic of today's
seminar is broad.
[MAHO in English]
The topic of today's seminar
is the artificial
intelligence revolution.
But before we delve
too much into that,
there's a thesis I'd like
to familiarize you with.
[MAHO] This paper was published
by a brilliant female researcher
from our university laboratory.
All of our memories are stored
within the cerebral cortex.
More specifically,
our histories are held
within the temporal lobe.
Our minds work as if they have
a computer's flash memory.
The brain sends
electrical signals
between neurons at
lightning-fast rates.
Ultimately, it is the pattern
of these electrical signals
which create and
reinforce memories.
They archive our pasts.
[MAHO] I regret to say
that the bright woman
who proposed this theory
passed away at the
young age of 18.
But using her theory
as a foundation,
we were able to construct
a monumental computer program.
That is a system that
preserves human memory
as electronic data.
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[MAHO] Though previous
systems fell short
of having real identities,
we've developed an
artificial intelligence
built with data drawn from
actual human memories.
Yes. It has feelings and
memories, just like a human.
AI with a brain and a heart.
The genius of Makise
Kurisu and her theory
enabled us to build this system.
Without further ado,
we would like to demonstrate
the AI named...
[MAHO]
...Amadeus.