[OKABE grunts]
[gasps]
[groans]
That's why you've got
to go back, Okabe!
It's a dream
and you have to wake up!
[OKABE gasps]
[feet pattering]
[whimpers]
[OKABE gasps]
It can't be!
Mayuri!
[panting]
--[MAYURI] Okarin?
--[gasps]
[DARU gasps]
You're finally awake.
Well, I'll be damned, buddy!
You had us all freaking out
when you just collapsed
for no reason like that.
I collapsed?
Really?
[OKABE] You mean,
Fubuki and I both collapsed?
-[MAYURI] Yeah.
-And to make matters even worse,
most of the hospitals
were shut down for the New Year.
[OKABE]
Huh, that is odd.
Did it work?
Am I back in
the original world line?
[MAYURI]
Here.
[gasps]
Makise Kurisu.
--[MAYURI] Huh?
--[BOTH gasp]
Do you know a Makise Kurisu?
Yep. I do.
[gasps]
That's the AI person you have
inside your phone, isn't it?
Amadeus, or something.
[OKABE] I wish
she wouldn't scare me like that.
Speaking of, how is Amadeus?
It wasn't completely hacked.
They're restoring it right now.
--Thing is...
--What else happened?
We also found out that a burglar
broke into Maho's hotel room.
And that's not everything.
There was an explosion
at the Wako City office.
They're not letting us in.
[OKABE]
What strange timing.
Makes me think someone
was orchestrating all of this.
Any clue who did it?
Not at all.
[OKABE] The attackers
from before, perhaps.
[KAEDE gasps]
Oh, wow, you're awake!
[MAYURI]
Has your fever come down?
[FUBUKI]
Mm-hmm. It's all gone now.
So, you're feeling better,
too, then, Okarin?
[OKABE]
Uh, yeah.
The doctors have been saying
that I might have
that new form of encephalitis
that's been going around.
But it's probably nothing
to worry too much about.
New encephalitis?
Yeah, it's something
that just popped up.
It gives people
a pretty high fever.
But still, why would you two
lose consciousness
at the exact same time?
Without some sort
of external stimulus,
the likelihood of that
is almost zero.
[KAEDE]
See? It has to be what I said!
Will you just drop it?!
What? What?!
Kaede's writing
a romance novel.
She thinks this means
Okabe and I must be soulmates.
Huh?
It's true, Fubuki!
When you first woke up,
all you wanted
to talk about was Okarin.
I told you that was just because
of the weird dream I had!
What dream?
It was so vivid and realistic.
But, Mayushii had been...
Huh?
Don't worry!
It was just a nightmare.
Not real at all.
But in it,
Mayushii was gone,
and I was working in the
May Queen café with Faris.
And then, Okarin came in,
and I had never met him.
[OKABE] She has memories
from the alpha world line.
Could it be
Reading Steiner?
[DOCTOR] Mmm, well,
your symptoms have all gone away
so that's great.
Let's schedule a follow-up
just to be safe.
I'd like to see you in a week.
--Sound good?
--Uh, sure.
[MAYURI]
I'm glad they let you leave,
aren't you, Okarin?
Fubuki has to stay
in the hospital
a little longer, though.
Don't worry!
She's a fighter,
she's gonna be all right!
[KAEDE]
You think?
Hey, Okabe?
Huh?
Why'd you bring up
Kurisu back there?
Oh, um, it's just that--
I had a strange dream
about her.
You did?
Hey, where did Hashida go?
Oh, Daru had to leave.
He told me he needed to take
care of something important.
[KAEDE]
Hmm?
[SUZUHA]
So, what else?
Meh.
Okarin wasn't showing
symptoms anymore,
so the doctors
let him go home today.
Fubuki and Okabe were
both present for the attack.
They collapsed
at the same time?
What was he like
when he regained consciousness?
Like the same brooding mess
he's been for a while now.
But he did say a name.
He mentioned Makise.
Makise?
[sighs]
See you guys!
[MAYURI] Yeah!
I'll text you in a little bit!
[MAYURI]
Here you go.
[MAHO]
Oh, thank you.
Now that I think about it,
what with the break-in
at my hotel
and the explosion
at the office,
I don't think I've eaten
anything since last night.
All we have here
is chicken tenders
and some bananas.
Oh, you want me
to go buy you a bento?
That's all right.
I'll eat something
later at the hotel.
You're going back?
[giggles]
The professor asked me
the same thing.
He said I should probably
move to a different one now.
He's right.
You'd be safer that way.
But I don't have any idea
where to stay.
With us?
[MAHO] I wouldn't
want to impose like that.
It's also worth considering
the attack happened here.
--It's no safer.
--[phone buzzing]
No news on the Wako attack.
--[MOEKA] Right.
--Huh?
[OKABE]
Eh... Ah!
Wh-Where did you
even come from?!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Is this a friend
of yours, Okarin?
[OKABE]
Uh, yeah.
--When did you--
--[text notification]
[OKABE] You've
been here this whole time?
I have.
[dishes rattle]
What's going on?
Why aren't you two talking?
[OKABE]
I know.
[MAHO]
Hmm?
--[door clicks]
--Coffee? What?
[door clicks]
Your guest left?
But she just got here,
and I was about
to offer her some coffee.
[OKABE] I'm back
in the right world line now.
[OKABE]
And I swear,
I will save it.
I vow to protect this world
where Mayuri gets to live,
and I will not resort
to time travel.
[OKABE] 'Cause I know this
is what Kurisu would want.
[OKABE]
It's the only choice.
Hiyajo.
Huh?
Do you think you could
possibly hold off
on finding another hotel?
I'm nursing an idea.
[FARIS] Meow, so that's why
you came to visit me?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
We think your flat
might be the safest place
for Maho to stay
for the time being.
This isn't fair!
I'm so sorry
to put you on the spot.
That's nice of you,
but it doesn't bother me, meow!
--Uh...
--I knew it!
Didn't I tell you?
I had no doubt Faris would be
willing to let you stay!
[FARIS] You can make yourself
at home in the guest room!
Stay forever!
I want you to live with me
for as long as you're in Japan.
Okay, Maho-meow?
--[giggles]
--[MAHO] "Maho-meow"?
[FARIS] We've got Kuroki here
to protect us, he's great!
--So we're super safe, meow!
--[MAHO] Kuroki...?
[FARIS] Wanna take a bath?
Or watch TV?
[MAHO]
Hold on, wait!
Now we can all rest easy!
Well, that depends.
Kagari is still
with Rukako, right?
Mmm. I just heard from them
a little while ago.
Ruka is committed to
making sure Kagari stays inside
and said not to worry.
[OKABE] I suppose
I've done all I can for now.
Next, I've got to figure out
who raided the lab,
and what they're really after.
--[phone buzzes]
--Huh?
Suzuha?
[SUZUHA]
I'm over here.
[SUZUHA] Sorry to make you
come all the way to the roof,
but it was necessary.
So, what's this about?
[SUZUHA]
Look, I'm terrible at this.
Verbal communication's
not my strong suit.
Forgive me if
I skip the niceties
and get straight to the point.
No complaints here.
Did you experience
a recent world line change?
[OKABE]
What would make you ask me that?
[SUZUHA]
The nature of the situation.
In addition to what
you've told me before
about Reading Steiner
and whatnot.
[OKABE]
What happens if I say yes?
[gasps]
You may not
understand this,
but it means
a great deal to me.
Suzuha...
Now, then.
I order you to tell me,
Okabe Rintaro!
I'll ask you one more time.
Have you experienced
a world line change?
Is this a different world line
than the one we were in before?
[OKABE]
Don't worry. Everything's okay--
we're still in
the same world line.
[SUZUHA]
Is that the truth?
[OKABE]
Yes.
We shifted to a different one
for a bit, but now we're back.
At least, as far as I can tell.
So you're admitting
that something did shift.
[OKABE] Yes, but I have
no idea what caused it.
The earthquakes in Russia.
Huh?
[SUZUHA] Those have nothing
to do with nuclear testing.
They're the result
of America and Russia
racing to invent time machines.
Sooner or later,
that competition is going
to spark the beginning
of World War III.
Maybe sooner than we think.
[OKABE]
Russia... and America?
The way he said it
was so distinct.
It's phonetic code.
What is phonetic code?
Used in the military.
Mostly in the western world.
[OKABE]
Is that what happened?
The earthquake?
I am such an idiot.
I was so concerned
about what to do,
but I never had
the time for all that!
[OKABE] Well,
what are you gonna do?
[SUZUHA]
I'm going back to July 28th,
and you're coming with me!
And if I won't?
[SUZUHA]
I won't give you that choice.
They're experimenting
with time machines as we speak!
What if the world line
keeps changing because of that,
and the path to reach
Steins Gate
gets blocked off forever?
[OKABE]
What if it's already too late?
[SUZUHA gasps]
Could you decide?
Could you make the choice
between two world lines
and know you'd done no harm?
Are you willing
to kill this world line?
To just let it dissolve
into the ether?
Shut up, now!
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE gasping]
You shot me...
I won't miss again.
[OKABE gasps]
[SUZUHA]
I am begging you.
[OKABE sighs]
July of 2010.
I realized that just by
using the Phone Wave,
I was able to send
messages into the past.
But in the end, the only thing
those d-mails achieved
was changing the world line,
and to restore the original one,
I convinced my friends
to destroy the only world
where they ever
felt safe and happy.
I ripped apart something
we'd crafted,
and I sacrificed more
than you could ever imagine,
just to bring this world
back to its rightful state.
And now, if I go back
to that summer,
the entire hellish nightmare
just replays itself!
[SUZUHA]
So you're content
to just let this world line
be what it is?
World War III is going
to burn the planet,
and billions of people will die!
There's no escaping it.
That's the way this world line
inevitably ends!
[OKABE] And what happens
if going back
only makes the situation worse?
No, that's not--
[OKABE] What if we're able
to change the world line,
but all that awaits us
is a future
even more
desolate and terrifying
than the one you came from?
[SUZUHA whimpers]
Even if we can change
the events of the past,
we can't manipulate the future
to be what we want.
[whimpers]
--[DARU] Suzuha.
--[gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Dad.
Gotta say,
I kinda figured
something like this
might go down.
What are you doing
with that gun?
[growls] You shouldn't have
to ask that, Dad.
We don't have
any time to waste!
We are on the precipice
of an all-out world war!
[DARU] Even if you forced
Okarin to come with you,
how could you be sure
it would solve anything?
[SUZUHA]
I don't know!
[DARU] From the moment I
started researching time travel,
one problem kept
coming back to me over and over.
Trying to control
the outcome of world lines
and manipulate
the law of causality
is too much for any of us.
[SUZUHA]
Then, what can we do?
Why do you think I'm doing
all this in-depth research, kid?
[SUZUHA whimpers]
Dad, I can't--
How about you just trust what
your dear old dad has to say
and behave accordingly,
for once in your life.
[SUZUHA gasps]
Just leave it all to me.
I'll figure something
out eventually.
Because, after all,
I am a super hacker!
[chuckles]
[SUZUHA gasps]
[sobbing] I'm lost.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know
what's right anymore.
[SUZUHA sobs]
I need help!
I can't--
I'm drowning!
[sobbing continues]
Please!
It's too much!
Help me!
Please, Dad!
[sobbing]
[OKABE] "On the precipice
of World War III."
[OKABE] I don't even know
if it's possible.
Can we alter the future
without time travel?
Or is that a Sisyphean task?
[MAKISE]
That's a tough one.
[gasps]
[MAKISE] But writing off
a notion as impossible
without exploring it fully
is the antithesis
of scientific inquiry.
[OKABE]
That's what you'd say...
...if you were here.
[metal scraping]
--[footsteps approaching]
--[BRAUN] Hmm?
Well? What's up?
Are you here to beg
for more time to--
[OKABE] I want to continue
our conversation from before.
[BRAUN]
You what?
Really?
[OKABE]
Yes.
[BRAUN grunts]
[BRAUN]
Can't say.
I don't have nearly
enough information.
[OKABE] If you know which
organizations use phonetic code
and could tell me,
that would be a start.
Well, there are thousands
of those in the west alone.
Although...
[OKABE]
Go on.
If that attack really
was carried out
by some organization,
I seriously doubt it was one
whose name is public.
It's either some fringe group
that makes sure their name's
kept under tight wraps,
or an entity that's perceived
as so innocent
no one would ever
suspect them of foul play.
For example?
Man, are you really
gonna make me answer that?
Whatever.
It's no skin off my back
whether you know or not.
All right, Okabe.
Assuming that every
part of the story
you've told me is true,
and I had to take
a wild shot in the dark here.
[keyboard clacking]
[OKABE]
D-U-R-P-A.
Defense Ultimate
Research Projects Agency.
Created by the Department
of Defense
as a military research entity.
And Stratfor.
A private American
policy institute.
Almost like a shadow CIA.
Focused on predicting
large-scale terrorism.
If the basis for Russia's
time machine research
is Dr. Nakabachi's paper...
[MAKISE]
Hold on, excuse me?
That's called stealing,
you know.
[OKABE] And the Americans
connect all the dots,
then it would lead them straight
to Makise Kurisu and Amadeus!
[MAKISE] In that case,
why wouldn't they just raid
Viktor Chondria University?
It would be pretty easy to hack
into the research computers.
Why take the trouble
to come all the way here?
[OKABE] When
those people raided the lab,
they wanted Kagari.
Is that because
she's from the future?
You think they came
for the time machine
that brought her here?
[MAKISE] Even if
that is what they're after,
it doesn't mean they'll find it.
Why not?
[MAKISE]
If their time travel research
was based on a time machine
from the future,
it would create
a massive temporal paradox.
That can never happen.
[OKABE]
Right, so that means--
[MAYURI] A burglar broke
into Maho's hotel room.
And that's not everything.
There was an explosion
at the Wako City office.
They're not letting us in.
[OKABE gasps]
Is that what's going on?
[DARU]
Know what I think?
Pretty soon Okarin is going
to have to take up command.
He's our leader,
whether he likes it or not,
and we're gonna need him
to show us the way soon.
[SUZUHA]
Hey, what time is it?
It's just about
the ass crack of dawn now.
Do you think that he'll get in?
[DARU]
Hmm?
You know, Uncle Okarin.
Into the time machine.
When it comes down to it,
I know he will.
And once that happens,
Hououin Kyouma
will respawn once more!
Like a phoenix from the ashes,
he will rise,
in all his delusional glory!
Because,
at the end of the day,
the Future Gadget Lab
only exists
because Okarin wanted it to.
[SUZUHA chuckles]
Dad.
Do you have any awareness
of how embarrassing
you sound right now?
[DARU]
Oh, damn.
You're right, I sound lame,
and I would rather die
than say any of that
to his face, too.
[chuckles]
You know what?
I'm gonna write a letter.
I think I owe Uncle Okarin
an apology for earlier.
I'll say sorry,
then leave it at that.
[DARU]
That's a good idea.
And while you're at it, why
not write one for Daddy, too?
You could throw in
some cute photos!
[chuckles]
Maybe, if I feel like it.
Hey, now,
why does Uncle Okarin
get special treatment?
[SUZUHA]
Well, I kind of shot him.
Anyway, this is
no time for pouting.
Because Russia's already
started experimenting
with time machines?
Well, that is a factor,
but it's more about the fuel.
I wasn't conservative.
I used far too much
in my search for Kagari.
Isn't there any way
to switch out the battery?
Negative.
I had Faris bring me
one of those huge batteries
they put in big trucks,
but it died in no time.
There's no other fuel source.
[DARU]
Bummer.
How much more can we jump?
Half a year,
maybe once or twice,
but no more than that.
And that's if we're lucky.
What would happen if
the battery died during travel?
Who knows.
But, if I had to take
a wild guess,
I'd say we'd lose control
and get trapped
beyond the event horizon
for all of eternity.
Don't even say that out loud,
you're gonna jinx it!
[laughs softly]
Yeah, sorry.
[SUZUHA]
Although...
I am curious
what that would be like.
[SUZUHA] What if it feels
as peaceful as it does
in this moment,
but it lasts forever?
If it did,
that wouldn't be so bad.
--[door clicks]
--[OKABE] Hiyajo--
[MAHO]
What's the matter?
Um, what happened in here?
It's a disaster zone.
Disaster?
In my opinion, it's quite
peaceful and comfortable, sir!
[OKABE] Hold on,
you've only been here one day.
It's too dangerous
to venture outside.
I've been forced to conduct
my research in here.
So why have you come?
Uh, well...
You mean to tell me Kurisu
was researching time travel?
Yeah, I think
this all stems from that.
They want any trace
of her research.
My guess is her theories
are in Amadeus,
so they hacked it.
[gasps]
Do you know if
there's anything else?
Like data?
Or notes on her research
that might be dangerous
in the wrong hands?
If there are,
it might get us closer
to answers about the attack.
I know of...
...nothing.
I understand.
♪
I can't... tell him.