[OKABE panting]
[OKABE]
Don't panic.
The world line
clearly hasn't changed.
Which means
Mayuri and Suzuha
must still be okay.
Or here and alive, at least.
[groaning]
[ALEXIS]
Howdy, Rintaro.
[OKABE]
Professor Leskinen?
[SUZUHA]
Mayuri!
--[SOLDIERS gasping]
--[SOLDIER B] Reyes?
[KAGARI]
What've you done to my mommy?
[SOLDIER B]
Huh?
[gasps]
[thud]
[SOLDIER C gasps]
Engage!
[SOLDIERS groaning]
[SOLDIER F grunts]
[SOLDIER G whimpering]
[COMMANDER]
Stay alert!
[SOLDIER G grunts]
[grunting]
[choking]
--[gasps]
--[COMMANDER] Aim for the body!
Slow her down!
[groaning]
Kagari, no!
[gasping]
It's noisy out there.
Aren't you a bit curious
about that?
What are you talking about?
Of course!
Why are you even here right now?
[ALEXIS] It's bad manners
to answer a question
with more questions, Rintaro!
Minus ten points for style.
Oh, well.
I am surprised that you
showed up here so quickly.
So, who was it?
Which one of your little friends
gave you the big tip-off?
[chuckles]
[ALEXIS]
Maho? No.
I suppose if I had to guess,
I'd say, Kurisu.
Wait, Kurisu? [gasps]
[OKABE]
Of course.
I guess, to Amadeus,
the professor who created
the system that spawned them
would be both father and God.
[laughs]
Did she actually
call me something
as flattering as all that?
Does have a nice ring to it.
[ALEXIS]
Surely inflates one's ego,
to be praised as a god
by such a superior intellect.
Yes, well, that's not
the only hint she gave us.
"Our most secret domains
have been unveiled.
Thus, we may tell
Father the secrets
of manipulating time,
and where to find them."
[ALEXIS]
You're really quite dense,
aren't you, Rintaro?
If you were able
to interpret that message,
then you shouldn't have to ask
what I'm doing here.
[OKABE gasps]
[ALEXIS]
I hate to break it to you,
but you're in over your head.
Answer me this.
Who the hell are you?
Just a scientist.
You see, science isn't always
a righteous endeavor
for the greater good.
I presume you've likely heard
of a little company
called Strategic Focus?
[OKABE]
Strategic--
You mean Stratfor?
A private intelligence agency
often called
the "Shadow CIA,"
and less flattering names.
[OKABE] So, it's been you
from the beginning!
[ALEXIS]
America, Russia.
All the great powers
will escalate conflict
in pursuit
of the time machine,
and that race commences
this very day, my friend.
[OKABE gasping]
[ALEXIS] I couldn't exactly
take action before this point,
because of the particular way
everything had to converge.
I've been itching
with excitement,
and now the moment
has finally arrived.
I take it you know exactly
what I'm getting at.
Right, Rintaro?
[OKABE]
What the hell is going on?
How does he have
all this knowledge?
Was it Hiyajo?
I can't believe she would--
No, she couldn't.
All Kurisu's memories
stored within Amadeus
are from before
she came to Japan.
Then who could it have been?
[ALEXIS laughing]
The look on your face
is priceless
and tells me
that you're wondering
how I came to possess
this information.
Had to be someone, right?
One who knows it all,
a time-traveling
little messenger
came to the past to help me.
Kagari!
[MAYURI whimpers]
[SUZUHA]
You're gonna be all right.
I will?
Thanks.
[crying]
Just don't move.
Luckily the ricochet
only grazed you,
but you're still losing
a lot of blood.
That's not good.
Don't watch that!
[COMMANDER A grunts]
[SOLDIER H gasping]
[gun clicking]
You hurt her.
[SOLDIER whimpering]
Mommy.
Why would you hurt...
...my Mommy?!
--[gunfire]
--[OKABE gasps]
Oh, my, are they still
at it out there?
I thought I instructed them
not to make too
much of a ruckus.
[OKABE grunts]
[ALEXIS]
Dammit!
[gun clattering]
[OKABE groaning]
[gasps]
Mayuri! I'm right here!
[OKABE gasps]
Kagari?
[SUZUHA]
Don't, Mayuri, stay back!
What did... she do...?
--[OKABE] Mayuri!
--[KAGARI gasps]
[whimpering]
[KAGARI cries]
[KAGARI]
Mommy.
I'm sorry.
I had to because they--
Those bad men tried to hurt you!
--[KAGARI groans]
--[OKABE gasps]
Mommy. Don't cry.
I wish you hadn't
seen me like that.
Kagari!
[SUZUHA cries]
--[KAGARI] Mommy...
--[OKABE] Try to stay still.
Suzuha.
[OKABE]
How's Mayuri?
Her head's a bit scratched up
from the bullet, but she's fine.
No other injuries,
I don't think.
She's safe.
Your mommy is okay.
Yeah?
I'm so grateful.
Please, don't try to talk.
It's okay.
There's nothing to worry about,
'cause despite how it may look,
I'm not in any pain at all.
I don't feel anything bad.
You don't have to be tough.
You can just--
[KAGARI]
I hear the voice of God,
speaking lovely thoughts to me.
He tells me that
it doesn't hurt.
He tells me that I
don't have to suffer.
And that's why it doesn't--
[KAGARI coughs]
[OKABE]
Please! Try to stay calm!
[MAYURI]
Come with me.
[SUZUHA gasps]
[MAYURI]
Hi, Kagari.
Mommy?
I missed you so much.
[SUZUHA]
Kagari.
Suzuha. My big sister.
I'm sorry.
Whenever I hear
the voice of God like that,
everything in my head
gets all messed up.
God tells me things
that he wants me to do,
and I just do it.
I'm sorry. I...
--[MAYURI] Kagari, no!
--[SUZUHA] Kagari!
[ALEXIS] Looks like I missed out
on the main event.
Too bad.
Brainwashing and enhancement
techniques from the future.
They're simply spectacular,
aren't they?
[OKABE]
It was you.
[SUZUHA]
You did this to Kagari?
[ALEXIS]
Not quite,
I'd say it was more
of a joint endeavor.
By me, yes, but also, by me.
I don't know what all your
cryptic BS means. Who cares.
I do know that
you're the one to blame
for all the terrible things
that happened to her!
You're certainly
right about that.
[SUZUHA grunts]
[SUZUHA gasping]
I should just slit your throat.
I'm not sure why you stopped,
but thank you.
Suzuha. I'm sorry.
--[gun cocks]
--[SUZUHA gasps]
No, stop!
Professor.
[ALEXIS laughing]
Maho, isn't this crazy?
I'll bet you can't even
believe your eyes.
But this was all preordained
to happen, so, don't worry,
there was no way
you could have stopped it.
What do you mean,
"preordained"?
[ALEXIS]
Observation and keen insight.
Those qualities are what
set us scientists apart.
Didn't you hear?
This was a joint endeavor.
Between me and myself.
One that subverted time.
There's no way.
It can't be.
Thirteen years ago,
our sweet Kagari contacted me
of her own free will,
or so I thought.
You couldn't even imagine
what that little girl
said to me.
[KAGARI] I hear the voice
of God in my head.
[ALEXIS]
The voice of God?
[KAGARI] It's the future
you inside my head.
So, God's voice.
It was you.
[ALEXIS laughing]
Exactly right.
It sounds completely insane.
My future self did me a favor
and sent Kagari back
into the past to find me.
All so I could somehow obtain
the power to manipulate time.
You sent her here
to do your bidding?
In other words,
she was your pawn.
And what a good little pawn
she turned out to be.
It was an intricate plan
to track the movements
of the resistance
you will form
in the distant future.
The future me trained
countless young girls and boys
to act as emissaries
and infiltrate your ranks.
You're all so soft-hearted,
you fell for it,
even more quickly
than I anticipated.
[ALEXIS laughs]
Then there was the pinnacle
of my plan, my fail safe.
If you managed
to escape to the past,
in one way or another,
I was still protected.
[SUZUHA gasps]
I made sure to send
a little messenger along
to contact my past self
using brainwashing techniques.
[classical music plays]
[ALEXIS] I found it quite hard
to believe initially.
But as I conducted my own
research into the matter,
I began to realize
that her story
checked out at every turn.
I came to the conclusion
that the time machine was real,
and that Kagari had truly come
from the future, as she claimed.
You mean, you created Amadeus
because Kurisu--
Correct.
Because Kurisu was destined
to get herself killed,
I was forced
to create a system
that would preserve
her precious data,
especially that genius time
travel theory of hers.
That's the only thing
you cared about?!
You're heartless!
You could have stopped her
from dying, but you didn't!
[ALEXIS]
Everything I did,
all the long,
tiresome groundwork,
was leading to this,
the day I steal
the time machine.
To defy causality
and overcome convergence.
It was all the grand,
master plan
of my brilliant future self.
A way for me to shape the world
exactly to my liking.
How could you go that far?
And once you had stolen
the time machine,
what did you plan to do then?
[ALEXIS]
Rintaro.
What kind of scientist worth his
salt would ask that question?
The thing about people like us
is that we experiment
in the hope
that our hypotheses are right.
We observe the world to prove
we know how it works.
My future incarnation
constructed a theory,
and my past self set out
to prove its accuracy.
No more to it.
Just what I've always done,
you see.
Don't you realize you'll
create a time paradox?
Or maybe you just
don't care for this world
and have no qualms
destroying it.
[ALEXIS] If that sort
of thing does happen,
I would love to see it
with my own eyes.
[laughing]
[remote clatters]
Well, she's dead, so I guess
that means the brainwashing,
as helpful as it was,
didn't make her bulletproof.
[ALEXIS laughing]
You sicken me.
You are nothing but a
disgusting sociopath!
[chuckles]
[laughing]
This from the man
who once paraded around
calling himself
a mad scientist!
Now, would you mind stepping
out of my way, please?
[ALEXIS] This roof will be a
battlefield before too long.
And this time machine is going
to be at the center of it all.
Then you'd better go.
[ALEXIS] I'm sure you haven't
forgotten about Nakabachi
and his paper in Russia,
and then there's
the intelligence
I myself handed over to Stratfor
regarding this
miraculous device, as well.
This escalating information war
leads to both sides
meeting to battle here
on this very rooftop,
and today, of all days.
History tells us
that the time machine
gets destroyed
in that skirmish
and the machine
won't exist again
until 25 years from now
when it's recreated,
based on the initial theory.
But then, what if someone
just so happened to steal it
and get away
in the nick of time?
What if they staged
its destruction
and escaped
into the past instead?
[SUZUHA] Are you telling us
your entire plan?
[ALEXIS] It's been ten or so
years since I first met Kagari.
That's quite a long time.
[ALEXIS] I've come this far,
and now it's time to--
[KAGARI]
I hear the voice again.
It infiltrates
my innermost thoughts.
The voice of my God.
[gun cocks]
You can't stop me.
[SUZUHA grunts]
--[gunshots]
--[ALEXIS gasps]
--[gunshot]
--[ALEXIS groans]
[SUZUHA screams]
[grunting]
[body thuds]
[blows landing]
[SUZUHA] Wake up,
you worthless piece of trash!
Kagari endured atrocities
a thousand times
worse than this,
and I will make you suffer
as much as she did!
--And worse!
--Stop it, Suzuha, no!
[SUZUHA]
Get up! You bastard!
I'll kill you!
[OKABE]
I said stop!
No! Let go of me!
--[DARU] Suzuha!
--[SUZUHA gasps]
[DARU]
That's enough, let him be.
But Dad...
If you murder him like this,
it makes you
no better than he is.
[SUZUHA sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
Huh?
[KAGARI groans]
[gasps] She's still alive.
Kagari!
[footsteps]
[MAYURI]
Can you hear me?
Look, Suzuha's here.
It's the same hand
that held mine.
Back then, when I was a scared
little girl, all alone.
It feels-- It feels so warm.
[SUZUHA]
Kagari.
My big sister.
Suzuha, I'm so sorry
for everything.
I'm sorry.
Kagari!
[SUZUHA sobbing]
It's not fair.
Why did it have to come to this?
[helicopter blades whirring]
Oh shit!
Incoming!
[rapid gunfire]
Mayuri!
It's okay!
She isn't injured.
[COMMANDER B]
Locate the professor.
[helicopter blades whirring]
This is it.
--Suzuha, let's go!
--[SUZUHA gasps]
[MAYURI]
He said the time machine
will be destroyed soon, right?
[gasps]
We have to get out of here
before then!
Come on.
We can change the future!
Is that DURPA?
We've got to do it now,
for Kagari!
[OKABE gasps]
Get in!
No! Wait! Mayuri!
[OKABE grunts]
Okarin!
Don't do this!
Why do you feel like
you have to be the one
to make this sacrifice?
I beg you. Stay with me!
[MAYURI]
I have to go,
and you won't
convince me not to!
This is all part of--
Operation Arclight,
to save my world!
Arclight?
But I don't know--
[SUZUHA]
Mayushii, come on!
[OKABE]
Mayuri! Don't go.
Please, Mayuri!
Bye, kid.
Dammit! They're stealing it,
secure the target!
--[rapid gunfire]
--[SOLDIERS groan]
[DARU groaning]
For real? This is happening
in modern-day Tokyo?
Don't leave me...
--Here we go.
--Right!
[engines humming]
[beeping]
Mayuri!
[explosion]
This is part of
the time machine.
I guess they didn't make it out.
Suzuha...
[OKABE crying]
Mayuri.
Okabe?
[OKABE sobbing]
[OKABE]
Mayuri!
[door slams]
[OKABE]
Mayuri.
Mayuri!
[OKABE]
[keys clacking]
[MAHO]
It's not finished yet!
[OKABE]
Why?
Why did it happen like this?
Okarin.
--[OKABE yells]
--[thud]
[OKABE crying]
I did it.
I'm the one who chose
this world line
because I thought it was
the best way to keep her safe!
But I couldn't.
This world line was built
on Kurisu's sacrifice.
That was supposed to mean
I wouldn't have
to lose Mayuri again.
And yet, it happened anyway.
Why did she do this?
Tell me!
[phone vibrating]
Mayuri?
[MAYURI]
Dear Okarin,
Hi! Too-too-roo!
It's me, Mayushii!
The truth is, I wanted to tell
you all this in person,
but I didn't know
if I'd have the courage
to get it all out.
Plus, I was worried you
might try to stop me,
so I decided it'd be better
to say it this way.
I'm taking the time machine
to the past with Suzuha.
You'll probably
be really upset
and wondering
why right about now.
But this is just something
that I know I have to do.
Because that day,
I was the one who did it.
Before then, no matter
how bad things got,
my strong Hikoboshi would
always pick himself back up
with that huge, crazy laugh.
I'm the one who hid him behind
all those dark clouds.
But you see,
I believe I was wrong.
Nobody was ever pushing
the full responsibility
of repairing the future
onto you alone.
Steins Gate is something
that we all have to work
to find together.
We're all with you,
fighting alongside you.
Daru is there,
and Suzuha is, too.
Ruka and Faris and Yuki
are all in your corner,
doing everything they can.
And now we even have another
brilliant scientist,
Maho, on our team.
It's my turn to do my part.
After all,
I am Future Gadget
Lab Member 002,
and this will be
my very first big mission!
[MAYURI] I'm sure that you're
going to worry about me
a whole lot, but I
think it'll be okay.
Besides, I know in my heart
that if something bad
were to happen,
you would be right there
in a flash to save the day!
The Hououin Kyouma
that I've always adored
will come swooping
to rescue me
in a brand new,
shiny time machine!
That's why I've decided to go.
I promise that
I'll come back someday.
So please, wait for me?
[MAYURI]
And know this.
I love Hououin Kyouma.
But guess what?
I love Okabe Rintaro even more!
More than anything!