[YUKI]
A Christmas party?
Yep. Everyone's coming
to the lab to hang out.
And it would mean
the whole world to me
if you guys could be there, too.
Even me?
We're all invited?
Sure! I wouldn't bring it up
in front of you if you weren't.
I'd never leave my
cosplay buddies out.
It's a Christmas
party after all,
so the more the merrier, right?
I'm making Santa costumes
for you, so come on!
Whoa! Seriously?
You'd make us Santa suits
even though you're working
so hard on Winter ComiMa?
[MAYURI giggles]
[MAYURI] Yeah, your costume
designer is going all out!
I'm making get-ups
you'll love, so be ready!
[FUBUKI squeals] That's my
future wife! I love ya!
Fubuki's so enthusiastic.
[YUKI] Hey, you should
make a Santa costume
for yourself to wear, too!
But I'm the designer.
I don't usually wear the clo--
Objection! I'm with Yuki.
We want to see you wearing
one of your own creations.
Uh...
That's right! And besides,
I know someone else
who wants to see
you dress up, too!
Okabe!
[MAYURI]
What do you mean?
Well, isn't he your...?
[FUBUKI]
Yeah, he's your boyfriend!
Wait, what? No, he's not.
Okarin and I haven't ever
liked each other that way.
Sure you haven't.
You two get along
so effortlessly.
If you're not dating,
you should be.
Seriously, we're not.
Because...
Okarin, uh...
Well, he likes somebody else.
[BOTH gasp]
Are you sure?
[MAYURI]
Mm-hmm.
The two of us do
get along really well,
but that's because
we grew up together,
like siblings!
[OKABE] I thought I told you
never to call me during class.
[AMADEUS] Yeah, that's why
I called you on your break
between classes.
--[OKABE] Wait, you--
--I took it upon myself
to peruse the schedule
on your school's website.
I knew you were ignoring me.
Uh--hey! I have quite the
full plate at present.
[AMADEUS]
Oh, yeah? What's on it?
It's impolite to pry.
This is so embarrassing.
Plan out your excuses, at least.
Jeez, why the harangue?
If I don't answer when you
call, it means I'm busy.
[AMADEUS] I'm only bugging
you to hold you accountable
for your promise.
What promise is that?
You don't remember?
This little lab of yours.
You said you'd take me there.
Look, we may call it a lab,
but it's more like a purlieu.
[AMADEUS]
Still.
The original me spent
quite a lot of time
there, didn't she?
[OKABE]
Well, I...
Hey, you don't have
to be evasive.
Answer me! [gasps]
I have to take this. Goodbye.
Hello, Mayuri.
[MAYURI gasps]
Okarin?
I have some exciting
news for you!
Fubuki and the others said
they can come to
the Christmas party!
Really? Well, I'm glad.
[MAYURI]
Oh, one more thing.
I bought a ton of supplies
to make some costumes
for the girls,
and I was wondering,
would it be too much trouble
for you to help me carry
it back to my place?
[OKABE]
Not at all.
Can I meet you at the lab
after my lecture period?
Yep! I'll be waiting
for ya! [giggles]
[MAYURI]
I got Okarin to come to the lab!
[FARIS]
Great! That's purr-fect!
[MAYURI]
The only one left now is Suzuha.
Does she know about it?
[MAYURI] Mmm, but that doesn't
guarantee she'll be there.
[FARIS] Isn't she always
at the lab anyway?
[MAYURI]
Yeah, usually,
but whenever
anyone else shows up,
she always runs and hides.
[FARIS] It'll all work out!
Don't you worry, meow!
Leave it to me!
This kitty's got your back!
[AMADEUS gasps]
So this is Akihabara?
It's uncouth to stare
at your phone and walk.
Hanging up.
[AMADEUS]
Hold on! If you switch around
to the back-facing
camera, I can see!
Okay!
[AMADEUS giggles]
[AMADEUS gasps]
Is that a--never mind.
It's not nearly as clean
as I imagined it would be.
[AMADEUS]
Radio Building?
Uh--hey! Don't cover it up!
Ugh. Come on!
--[BRAUN grunts]
--[NAE gasps]
Ah! Been a while, Okabe.
Hello, science guy!
Nice to see you both.
[AMADEUS]
Who's that?
Quiet in there.
Man, times sure have changed.
You're a legit
college student now,
not some wannabe scientist.
Keep up the good work, champ!
[AMADEUS] Wow! Were you
that much of a weirdo?
[OKABE]
Please shut up.
Huh?
I kept my promise.
[AMADEUS]
This is the lab?
It's a pig sty.
Is that really all
you've got to say?
[AMADEUS]
Oh, allow me to rephrase.
Why is it all
cluttered with junk?
[groans]
[AMADEUS] Laboratories
tend to be messy as a rule,
but this is absurd.
Do you get anything done?
I told you it
wouldn't be anything
like the labs you're
accustomed to.
[AMADEUS] Yeah, but you didn't
say it'd be a train wreck.
This place gives Maho's
room a run for its money.
Should one divulge her
friend's private habits
so thoughtlessly?
I was only hoping to win
support for my campaign.
Tell that girl to clean her room
every once in a while, 'kay?
Uhh... I'd rather not anger a
bona fide leviathan, thank you.
[AMADEUS chuckles]
Anyway.
I've always dreamed of
sharing a space like this
with a group of friends.
[OKABE gasps]
Where we all had our own sets
of personalized forks
and spoons and stuff.
[door opens]
You got over here sooner than
I thought you would, Okarin.
Too-too-roo! Huh?
Are you listening to music?
[AMADEUS]
Is that one of your friends?
I'd love to meet--
--[OKABE] Hanging up.
--[AMADEUS gasps] Hey, I--
Oh, you were on the phone?
[OKABE]
Yeah, but no worries.
You did mean a ton of stuff.
What's all this for, anyway?
[MAYURI giggles]
All the girls'
costumes for ComiMa
and their Santa get-ups
for the party!
[OKABE]
The Christmas party?
So is everyone coming?
[MAYURI]
Mm-hmm!
Fubuki, Kaede, and
Yuki are, for sure.
And Ruka and Faris are, too!
Yuki's coming?
Yeah! Of course she is.
You know what I think?
Yuki and Daru would
make the perfect couple.
They should get together!
Fubuki was like,
"No way, never gonna happen!"
But why not?
[SUZUHA] Our first mission is
to find this little guy, got it?
[KAGARI]
Huh? Oh, uh, okie-dokie.
[SUZUHA]
Good answer.
[SUZUHA giggles]
--[door opens]
--[gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Oh, Rumi, it's only you.
[FARIS]
Mm, did you say "Rumi"?
Nobody calls me that.
I'm Faris! Meow, meow.
[FARIS] Listen, if you
don't come to the lab
once in a while,
people get worried, you know?
[gasps]
[SUZUHA stammering]
If I go there, my mo--
I mean--
I prefer to be
alone, that's all.
I brought you some treats.
All your favorite little
kitty snacks, meow.
They'll keep until tomorrow,
so take your time
and enjoy them, okay?
[SUZUHA]
Thank you.
How is Daru's time machine
research coming along?
Seems really hard.
[SUZUHA] He's learning
a lot, but still...
[FARIS]
I'm sure he'll figure it out.
[SUZUHA] Sorry to put you
through all this trouble.
It's no trouble.
I just rent the building's
top two floors
to make sure no one
pokes their whiskers
around your research.
[SUZUHA]
Are you kidding?
Honestly, I owe you
more than I could ever
dream of paying back.
[FARIS giggles]
Don't you worry about it, meow!
If that's what it takes
to save the earth's
elementals from Byakhee,
then I'll do it wholeheartedly.
I will pounce on any
opportunity to help!
Uhh, okay!
I don't quite follow
all that, but thank you.
[FARIS] For Mayu and Dad--
for everyone's sake,
I have to convince Uncle
Okarin to come with me
to the entrance of Steins Gate.
[FARIS]
Huh?
[MAHO]
The 24th? That's Christmas Eve.
Can't we do it some other time?
[ALEXIS] Okabe said it wouldn't
be a problem to meet then,
so I figured we should.
Why, do you have a hot
Christmas date planned?
No, I don't, but you
wouldn't hear if I did.
Well, why not get a Santa outfit
and make a holiday affair of it?
'Cause in this country,
if you don't have a
date on Christmas Eve,
you're considered what the
kids call a "sad cat lady,"
and you wouldn't want that.
And Okabe doesn't want
to be a "sad cat boy."
Why does it always come
down to this subject?
That's the only thing you and
Amadeus ever want to talk about!
[ALEXIS]
Sorry. I get excited.
[MAHO]
Hm?
Aren't you curious to see
how their relationship
is developing now?
What's arisen between
her and Okabe?
[MAHO growls]
[ALEXIS]
You don't need to worry
from a security standpoint.
Because the system
operates using memories,
it's remarkably secure.
There's very little to fear.
[MAHO] But it's not
entirely without risk.
[ALEXIS]
Huh?
[MAHO] I have my own
concerns about it.
[phone vibrates]
What is it now?
[AMADEUS] Oh, is that
how you greet your friends?
[MAHO]
Security is the least of them.
I worry about Rintaro Okabe.
[camera clicks]
[AMADEUS] Are you
getting tired of this yet?
Uh--we haven't been
around that corner.
Let's check it out!
I refuse to be late to
my meeting because of you.
[AMADEUS]
C'mon, it'll only take a minute.
You still have 365 seconds
before they expect
you to be there.
Fine. Jeez!
[AMADEUS humming]
Are you having fun?
[AMADEUS]
Meh, i's frustrating
not being able to
move on my own.
[AMADEUS] I know. What if
you hooked up your phone
to some kind of
remote-controlled camera?
That way I could just--
No way.
[AMADEUS] Wow.
Why are you so vocal with me,
but on your group date,
you froze up?
What's up with that, huh?
[OKABE gasps]
Hey! How do you even--
[AMADEUS]
What? It's not my fault
you forgot to close the app.
I was listening in the
background the whole time.
It was hilarious. I lost it.
Your one-liners
were so awkward,
and who runs away when
the dating games start?
You totally ruined
Truth-or-Dare for everyone else.
Hold on just a second.
At this meeting with
the professor and Hiyajo,
are you gonna hand
over your logs?
Of course! And I'll include
every exchange I've overheard,
even accidentally.
[OKABE whimpers]
[AMADEUS]
You should know--
everything we've
ever talked about
is stored in the logs, too.
Like the fact that your
family runs a veggie market,
but you hate eggplant.
And how you called me
"Christina" when we first met,
which you still won't explain.
Please stop.
So tell me. Why Christina?
[OKABE]
Give it up.
[AMADEUS]
Human memories are vague.
As time passes,
new data comes pouring in,
and it all mixes together.
[OKABE]
Meaning what?
[AMADEUS]
Meaning that, unfortunately,
Amadeus is an incomplete
intelligence model
and that ambiguity is lost.
In other words, I can't forget.
[OKABE]
But wait.
The Amadeus in the
presentation could.
It forgot something.
[AMADEUS]
That's a programming process
where trivial logs
are made inaccessible,
but only from an
operational standpoint.
It's all backed up.
[OKABE] Which means
you'll never stop asking me
why I called you Christina.
[AMADEUS]
You'd better believe it.
[OKABE]
Such a persistent little AI.
You evaded the question,
which piqued my curiosity.
Don't you know what they say
about curiosity and the cat?
[AMADEUS] That's never stopped
researchers from investigating.
[ALEXIS]
Okabe!
--[ALEXIS laughing]
--[OKABE] Uh...
[OKABE] Sorry! I was here on
time. I just got distracted.
[MAHO]
What were you doing?
I didn't take you for
the loitering type.
[OKABE chuckles]
So, Rintaro, tell me what
you think of our Kurisu.
She's a bit bewildering.
I know she's an AI, and yet...
[ALEXIS]
Understood.
Sounds like you've got
a lot of great info to share.
I was planning to head over
to the college after this...
[AMADEUS]
Psst! Ma'am!
--Huh?
--Hey, ma'am!
Just go for it!
Now's your chance.
Christmas Eve is the
perfect opportunity to--
[OKABE]
I can't tonight.
I wish I could,
but I've got prior plans.
I promised a friend I'd
go to her Christmas party.
A party?!
[door opens]
[SUZUHA gasps]
Oh, hi, Dad.
[ALEXIS]
Wowzers!
What an awesome lab! So sparkly!
Hello, there! Thank you for
letting us crash your party,
Miss... Japanese maid girl?
--[FARIS meows]
--Sorry, kitty girl?
So, um, who are your friends?
[OKABE]
More like colleagues.
Professor Leskinen
and Maho Hiyajo.
I met them both
at the university.
Are you sure that we're welcome?
Because I'm feeling
super awkward right now.
If Rintaro says we're welcome,
"it's all good in the hood,"
like you kids say!
He didn't mean it!
He was just being polite,
but you pressed him!
Plus, no one says "it's all
good in the hood" anymore!
[ALEXIS]
What? You don't want to be here?
No! That's not what
I'm saying, Professor.
Hi! What grade are you in?
[MAHO sighs]
Oh, I'm an adult.
I know I don't look like it,
but I am! [chuckles]
[NAE gasps]
[OKABE sighs]
[ALEXIS] This lab of yours is
as merry as Santa's workshop,
but instead of elves, there
are beautiful girls everywhere!
Look at her!
That is one sexy Santa
in black, my friend.
That one's a dude.
[ding]
[MAYURI]
♪ Juicy tenders. ♪
♪ Our chicken's
number one! Yeah! ♪
They even made a special edition
family size just for Christmas!
Where's Suzuha? Is she coming?
Uh-huh.
Daru's out trying to
trick her into it right now.
He's tricking her?
Yep.
I hope he's able to come up
with a way to get her here.
[OKABE]
That just seems wrong.
[YUKI]
Yeah.
He said she wouldn't come
if she knew it was a party,
so he'd have to make up
some other story to tell her.
[OKABE]
That's a tall order.
She's not one to be
easily misled.
[MAYURI]
It's from Daru!
He says they'll both be here
in just a few minutes.
All right, everybody!
Time to get to your
hiding places.
[ALL]
Yeah!
[DAU] Whelp! Here I come,
a-rollin' into the lab
like I always do! Nothin' weird.
I've got Suzuha with me
and we're coming in!
[SUZUHA]
Dad! Stay back.
[DARU groans]
[ALL]
Merry Christmas!
--[YUKI gasps]
--[streamers popping]
Surprise, Suzuha! Welcome! Oh?
Uh, what?
[ALL gasp]
Uh...
Um, you okay?
Oh. It's you, M--
Suzuha! It's Christmas Eve!
This is a surprise
Christmas party, meow!
[MAYURI]
Yeah, just a party.
[SUZUHA]
Huh?
Uh, sorry if we scared you.
We were just trying to
make it a surprise!
--[YUKI chuckles]
--Uh... [sighs]
That explains why my Dad--
I mean, why my brother
was acting weird.
[MAYURI]
I'm sorry.
This whole party
thing was my idea.
Don't be. I'm the one
who should apologize.
This is a trip!
The lab looks
completely transformed.
[MAYURI] Yeah! Everyone
pitched in to help decorate.
Mayushii thought maybe a party
would help cheer you up,
so she's been working hard
to throw this together.
I see.
But the thing is,
I'm not really in a place where
I can relax and have fun.
I don't mind if you
all party without me.
[OKABE]
You should stay.
[gasps]
Enjoy yourself.
Yeah! Come on!
We're just eating food
and chatting, you know.
Why don't you hang out
with us for once,
stuff your face and be grateful
for the stellar company, yeah?
--[SUZUHA] Uh...
--[OTHERS laugh]
[FARIS]
All right, it's time to raise
a special Christmas toast, meow!
[ALL]
Merry Christmas! Cheers!
[phone vibrates]
Okarin?
We're about to start
opening presents.
Yeah. I'll be back in a flash.
Okay, my little kitties,
who wants to go first?
I know there's lots of
great gifts to choose from!
Don't be shy, meow!
[AMADEUS]
I've developed hypotheses.
[OKABE]
Prithee tell.
[AMADEUS]
Theory one:
your favorite American movie
star is named Christina,
and you were thinking about her,
so you called me
that by mistake.
[OKABE]
Wow, not even close.
[AMADEUS] Two: you had an
ex-girlfriend with the same--
[AMADEUS sighs]
[AMADEUS] Never mind.
Definitely not that one.
Uh--hold on!
[AMADEUS]
Oh, you've had a girlfriend?
Uh...
[AMADEUS]
I'll go ahead and take your
awkward non-response as a no.
[OKABE groans]
Silence, woman.
[AMADEUS]
Three:
you used to refer to the
original me as "Christina,"
either directly or indirectly.
Though the likelihood of
that seems kind of low.
[OKABE]
And why's that?
Because I know how I'd respond.
"That's not my name!"
--[gasps]
--Am I right?
[ALEXIS] Good, but get
a little bit closer.
Just a bit now. That's right.
Uh, okay.
--[camera clicks]
--It's not okay!
In fact, I'd call
it "actionable."
Oh, sorry.
--[MAHO gasps]
--What does that mean?
[MAHO] Oh, I'm not mad
at you, Nae. Not at all!
Don't worry. You didn't
do anything wrong.
They're adorable!
All is well within my
universe! [squeals]
Okabe's been out there a while.
Yeah, he has, huh?
Hold on, I'll go check on him.
[AMADEUS]
Did I get it?
Did you clam up
'cause I'm right?
[OKABE] Look,
stop jumping to conclusions.
[AMADEUS]
If you tell me, I won't have to.
[OKABE sighs]
[OKABE]
Do you really wanna know?
Is it that important?
[AMADEUS]
Yes.
[OKABE]
It was out of embarrassment.
I wasn't sure how to
pronounce your real name,
so I just made one up.
You just couldn't...
say my real name?
That's right.
[AMADEUS]
Uh--well, uh...
Thank you for telling me.
[OKABE]
Hold on, are you blushing?
[AMADEUS]
Uh--no! I am not!
What's the matter with you?!
If you think you can
catch me off guard
and rattle me by getting me
all sappy and sensitive,
then you'd better
think again, buddy!
--[OKABE laughs]
--Huh? What's so funny?
I don't know.
[AMADEUS]
What?!
It's just...
...that part of you
that I really...
[gasps] You...
[OKABE gasps]
[AMADEUS gasps]
Ma'am, I--
[OKABE]
Hiyajo, why'd you do that?
I told you.
It's easy to get deluded.
But make no mistake.
That isn't her. It's Amadeus.
Not the real Makise Kurisu.
[OKABE]
Yeah, I understand. I--
[MAHO] Because Makise
Kurisu... was murdered.
[MAHO]
She's dead.
Gone forever.
You hear me?
--Forever.
--[MAHO gasps]
[gasps]
[MAHO]
Okabe?
[OKABE gasping]
What's the matter?
Okabe!
[OKABE gasping]
[OKABE screaming]