[RUKA] All right,
we're off to the store.
Be back soon.
[MAYURI] If you think of
anything else we need,
just text me, okay?
Roger that.
[door closes]
[RUKA]
You don't have to come. Really.
[RUKA gasps]
Even if I didn't go,
it's not like I'd be
any help here. [chuckles]
Are we taking the long route?
[SUZUHA]
You lost all your memories?!
Yes.
So you can't remember
a single thing
that happened since we--
No way!
Look, Suzuha,
what makes you so certain
this is Kagari Shiina
in the first place?
I already told you that!
Because of the oopa!
It's the exact same one
I saw her mom give her.
It was Kagari's good luck charm.
She took it with her everywhere!
Where did you get yours, Kana?
I have no idea.
When they first found me,
it was the only thing I had.
I was clutching it,
even though I was unconscious.
You were unconscious?
[KAGARI]
Yes.
I guess I had collapsed
near the border of
the Chiba Prefecture
and a priest nearly tripped
over me lying in the path.
So, then, how'd you
end up at the shrine?
[KAGARI]
They felt it was inappropriate
for a girl to stay too long
at a practicing temple, so...
[SUZUHA]
She was at Ruka's!
Right under my nose
this whole time!
Tell me!
Is my name really
Kagari Shiina?
Do you know that for sure?
Can you two tell me
anything else about who I am?
--I need to--
--Wait. One thing at a time.
[KAGARI gasps]
Yes, I'm sorry.
Don't be.
When you hear the name
"Kagari Shiina,"
does it, perhaps,
bring back other memories?
No, not that I'm aware of.
And yet, it does give me an
intense, nostalgic feeling.
That girl who just
left with Ruka...
Do you mean Mayuri?
Oh, Mayuri?
Is that her name, then?
[KAGARI chuckles]
[KAGARI]
And mine is...
...Kagari Shiina.
[OKABE]
Kagari Shiina.
In 2036, she's...
...Mayuri's daughter.
[RUKA] So, just to
make sure I understand,
you're saying that Kana--
I mean, Kagari,
is somebody you know, Suzuha?
[SUZUHA]
Uh, yeah!
That's it, more or less.
[RUKA] Awesome! Do you
know where she lives?
Can you get in touch
with some of her family
and tell them she's okay?
Uh, I don't--I, uh...
Uh, well, Kagari moved to
a different neighborhood
when they were
still really young,
and Suzuha lost contact
with her at that point.
Oh, too bad.
Hey, at least we were able
to find out your real name.
That's something!
[sighs]
[MAYURI]
Hang on!
Kagari's real, full name is
Kagari Shiina, isn't that right?
Yeah, it is.
That means you and I
are alike in a way!
Because, you see,
my full name's Mayuri Shiina.
Mayuri Shiina?
Oh.
Ruka told me something about
you, but I couldn't believe it!
You have amnesia?
For real?
I do.
[MAYURI]
So that means...
...you don't remember
anything about who you are
or where you come from?
That's right.
[MAYURI]
Oh, wow.
Sorry.
That has to be really
painful for you.
Because it means
you can't remember
all the people you love
the most in the world.
Seriously.
Amnesia must be
the saddest thing
that could ever
happen to anyone.
It's heartbreaking!
So, um, if you ever
need help with something,
just tell me! I'd be happy
to do whatever I can!
I'm here, okay?
[KAGARI gasps]
Oh, hey! What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
Did I say something
I shouldn't have?
No, not at all.
I'm crying because I'm happy.
You really touched me just now.
I'm not the only one
who's here for you.
[KAGARI gasps]
[OKABE]
Mm.
Yeah. If you need me,
just ask, and I'm there!
Don't hesitate.
Thank you all. That means a lot.
[OKABE] It appears that we
found Kagari Shiina ourselves.
Where was she?
[OKABE] At a local shrine
where one of my friends lives.
But she was found unconscious
on the outskirts of Chiba.
Why there?
I have no clue.
She's suffering from
severe amnesia.
[MOEKA]
I see.
Any update on the
other search party?
Who they are?
[MOEKA]
No. Nothing yet.
[OKABE sighs]
No worries.
And I'm sorry, it's a busy
time of year as it is.
[MOEKA]
It's fine, work is work.
So what now?
Should I keep at it?
[OKABE]
If you don't mind.
It would be a great
help if you did.
[MOEKA]
Then I will.
That's that.
They found her.
[phone chimes]
[MAHO]
Hmm?
[MAHO sighs]
[footsteps]
--[REYES] Maho!
--[MAHO yelps]
[REYES giggles]
Professor! Not cool, come on!
Oh, wait. Were you messaging
with your boyfriend?
[MAHO]
He is not my boyfriend!
Why do you and Leskinen
keep harassing me about that?
The concept of love is
utterly useless, anyway!
Oh.
You couldn't be
more mistaken, Maho.
[MAHO gasps]
As a matter of fact,
I'm more passionate
about your love life
than any other field of study.
That'd be flattering
if it weren't weird,
but I'd rather you not
treat me like a test subject.
Anyway, I'm not the type
to be swept off my feet
by the inherently
delusional nature of love.
Really? What a shame.
Also, Professor?
[REYES]
Mm?
[KAGARI] So, um,
I'm sorry for all of this.
[MAYURI]
There's no need to apologize!
I'm here to help
with anything!
I meant what I said before!
Thank you.
I really do appreciate it.
Hey, Rukako,
do you have a second?
[RUKA]
You want me to try
to keep Kagari
from going outside?
That seems so...
[OKABE]
If she has to,
make sure someone
accompanies her.
And I can't say why.
Not right now anyway.
[RUKA]
I trust you.
It is weird, though.
[OKABE]
I'm sorry.
We still don't know who else
has been searching for Kagari,
and until we do,
it's prudent for us to
take every precaution
we possibly can.
[DARU]
In any case,
it's pretty amazing that we were
able to find Kagari, right?
So now you can relax, for once.
Yeah, I guess.
Okay, not exactly the relieved
response I was hoping for.
[SUZUHA]
That girl.
Where do you think
she's been all this time?
[DARU]
That is a good question.
[DARU] I've been wondering
about that part, too, actually.
But it's not like we can
force her to remember
and tell us everything,
you know?
Don't they say those memories
come back on their own,
out of nowhere?
All we can do now is be patient.
[SUZUHA]
Maybe.
But do we have that luxury?
[DARU]
Ooh, how 'bout this?
We could scare the crap
out of her to jog her memory.
Scaring chicks is
my strong suit!
Why--hey--
Wha--?
Why didn't it work?
It always works! [gasping]
[gasps]
[KAGARI] I won't let you
do something like that.
[KAGARI]
I hear... a voice.
[SUZUHA]
Kagari!
[gunshot]
Are you okay?
[DARU]
Hey, Okarin?
Aren't we supposed to be
going to the shrine right now
to celebrate the
New Year and stuff?
Uh, yeah, we are.
So, um, like, why are we stuck
in this awkward situation, then?
--[DARU whimpering]
--[BRAUN] Hey!
If you've got something to say,
then you'd better
speak up, nice and loud.
[DARU] No, we have
nothing at all to say, sir.
Oh?
Well, we were just hoping
we could get into
the lab, actually.
No way!
[DARU]
But why not?
Oh, such villainy!
Mr. Braun, we promised we
would meet the others here
to go to the shrine
for New Year's.
[KAEDE]
Sorry to keep you guys waiting!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[NAE giggles]
[BRAUN]
Nae, you're adorable!
Well, of course you are!
You're my daughter!
[BRAUN laughing]
Uh, Dad, you're hurting
me a little bit.
It's a good thing
she takes after mo--
Ahem.
I can't wait to go to
the shrine with everybody
and see Mayuri all dressed up
as a beautiful shrine maiden!
[BRAUN]
Yeah?
Well, listen to the girls
and behave yourself, got that?
[NAE]
Mm-hmm.
Oh, you're not coming with us?
[BRAUN] Nah, I got some
business to take care of.
If it weren't for that,
do you think I'm really be
leaving my precious daughter
with the likes of you?
Come on!
And let me be clear.
If anything happens to her,
you two will pay.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir!
[NAE]
I'll see you later, Dad!
Well, we'd better get
going, don't ya think?
Indeed.
But before we do anything else,
aren't we forgetting
something really important?
All together now!
[ALL]
Happy New Year!
[FUBUKI]
I can't wait to see Mayushii's
shrine maiden costume!
[KAEDE] No, silly. This is
a uniform, not a costume!
[FUBUKI]
Oh, that's right!
[YUKI] Isn't Suzuha
working with Mayuri today?
I bet they're having fun.
Look, a shrine maiden
for a sister is one thing,
but you might as well
dress her as a nurse, too,
and raise her moe so
much she gains a level.
Plus one die roll, baby.
Hashida's even more
perverted than I am,
which is saying something.
[OKABE]
Hey, um, thanks for coming.
I know Mayuri's the
one who invited you,
but then she got
herself talked into
working as a shrine maiden.
[MAHO]
It's okay. I don't mind.
'Cause there's something
I want to discuss with you.
[YUKI]
Oh, by the way,
didn't you say you're a student
at an American
university, Hiyajo?
[MAHO]
Hm? Yeah.
Your research sounded
really interesting.
But tell me again.
Was it aye-ayes?
Lemurs? Cool.
It's AI. Not aye-ayes.
[FUBUKI]
So no lemurs, then? Noted!
[YUKI] Right, she studies
artificial intelligence,
something I'm super
interested in, actually.
I would love to sit down
and have a chat with you
about it sometime!
[gasps]
[DARU]
Okarin!
You doin' okay, bro?
I'm good. It's
nothing. Shall we?
Hey, Okarin! Over
here, meow! [giggles]
[RUKA]
Oh, hey, everyone!
Happy New Year!
[ALL]
[DARU gasps]
[DARU] This is a
shrine maiden paradise!
Have I died and gone to heaven?
[YUKI]
Whoa!
[SUZUHA gasps]
Suzuha, you look lovely!
Oh, thank you so much.
You make a great shrine maiden.
Right?
[DARU]
Suzuha.
[SUZUHA gasps]
I want you to repeat after me.
"Bend over and drop trou, bro.
It's time for your
booster shot."
--[SUZUHA grunts]
--[DARU gasps]
[SUZUHA] What the hell
is the matter with you?
No wonder you're not getting
anywhere with Mom, you pig!
[DARU whimpers]
Uncle!
[YUKI laughs]
Oh, you two have such
a special relationship, huh?
Well, I mean, you know.
She is our daughter.
[DARU groans]
[SUZUHA chuckles]
Would you like to
offer some saké?
Or how about a fortune slip?
[SUZUHA chuckles]
No way. You're not--
What's wrong?
Did I do something bad?
Ruka is as beautiful as
ever, don't you agree?
[RUKA gasps]
You don't have to say that.
I refuse to believe this.
It's not true. I reject it.
It is the truth, sweetheart.
But if you need some proof,
we could show you.
Wha? Are you serious?
[FUBUKI chuckles]
What?
[RUKA screams]
[MAYURI giggles]
So, um, whatcha think?
It's great.
You look very nice.
Oh, really?
Thank you, Okarin!
She wouldn't accept it when
we told her the same thing,
'cause she just had
to hear it from you.
"What's he gonna say?"
--[MAYURI gasps]
--[KAGARI giggles]
[MAYURI] Hey, you weren't
supposed to tell him that part!
[KAGARI giggles]
Sorry about that.
[MAYURI]
Sheesh!
And you were
self-conscious, too!
Just as much as I was!
[KAGARI]
Uh--yeah, but...
I'm not as pretty.
Don't say that, Kagari!
You look beautiful in it!
[MAYURI]
Right, Okarin?
Huh? Of course!
You both look stunning.
[ALL laughing]
[DARU chuckles]
[YUKI giggles]
I'm kind of floored.
It's crazy. She's
just like Kurisu.
[OKABE]
You think?
[MAHO] Yeah, they're
identical... almost.
[OKABE]
I don't know.
I can't say I agree.
[sighs]
[MAHO] Anyway, I think
we understand each other.
About Amadeus, you mean.
Things can't go on
like they are,
or you won't ever get closure.
You need to make a choice
before work starts up
again after the holiday.
--I don't know.
--You have got to be kidding.
I've never actually
been to a shrine before.
Oh, thank you!
[laughs]
[MAHO groans]
Guess they couldn't
make it in time.
[OKABE]
Hm?
--[ALEXIS] Rintaro!
--[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
Professor?
Happy New Year,
Rintaro! [laughs]
I invited them,
because it's a special
occasion, and all.
[ALEXIS]
I thought this was a party.
Where are the Japanese
shaman girls?
[OKABE]
Shamans?
Oh, you mean the shrine maidens?
They're done working,
so they ditched the garb.
They just finished cleaning
and we were about to head out.
[ALEXIS]
Holy cow!
This is why I wanted
to get here earlier!
[REYES] You should
have thought about that
during your all-day
shopping spree.
Come on, let's go
visit the shrine.
No! You have to wash
your hands first.
[MAYURI]
Okarin!
Ruka's mom is so sweet.
She gave us a ton of
New Year's snacks!
Sorry if we kept you.
[REYES]
Rintaro! We'll see you around!
[OKABE]
Huh? Oh, leaving so soon?
He says the whole
point of coming here
was the shrine maidens.
Happy New Year! Bye!
[KAGARI]
Sorry!
That took longer
than I expected.
[NAE]
Yeah, it sure did!
I said sorry.
[OKABE]
Right-o, friends!
We should get going, ourselves.
[YUKI]
Oh, I wish I could.
I have to call it a day now.
You mean you're not coming
back to the lab with us?
They're short-staffed at work,
so I have to go in tonight.
Sorry, guys.
[MAYURI]
It's okay. Too bad.
I'll take a rain check,
and come back to play
with you some other time!
Well, shall we
head that direction?
Uh-huh.
Is everyone ready to
party till next year?
[ALL]
Yeah!
Let me heart it, guys.
One more time!
Here's to the best year
any of us have ever had!
[ALL]
Happy New Year to all of us!
Cheers!
[DARU]
Mmm! This zoni soup is tasty!
Really hits the spot!
[FARIS]
Thanks! It's from May Queen's
special New Year's
Menu, meow!
So, in other words,
I'm tasting a bit of Faris?
Only you could find a way to
make soup perverted, Hashida.
These beans are so delicious,
and they're packed
with nutrients, too.
Here you go, Nae.
Have as much as you want!
Candied chestnuts in
mashed potatoes, yum!
Um, guys, there's no way
I have room for all that food!
[giggles]
Hey, if you don't eat,
you won't grow! Chow down!
[DARU] Okabe, you're
too skinny! Eat more!
[OKABE]
What are you, my grandmother?
Oh, no. We ran out
of tea so fast!
Sure did.
We can make a quick run
to the store and get some.
Huh?
[KAEDE gasps]
Hello, sir!
[FUBUKI]
It's the landlord dude!
You're back from
the shrine already?
So where's everyone else?
They're all upstairs
at the party.
The two of us are
going to get more tea.
Oh, yeah?
I'll pop by to pick up
Nae a little later, then,
but could you get a message
to Okabe for me?
Have him text me
when the party's over.
[KAEDE]
Yes, sir, of course.
[BRAUN grunts]
[FARIS]
That's right, meow!
--[phone vibrating]
--[FARIS giggling]
[RUKA]
What about this one?
[FARIS]
Ooh, try it, it's really good.
I think it's my fave, meow.
[gasps] Hello, ma'am!
Where have you been all night?
Hold on. Are you
where I think you are?
Whoa! That looks awesome!
[AMADEUS gasps]
[FARIS]
What is it? Video chat?
[AMADEUS]
Uh, kind of, but not quite.
[OKABE gasps]
[FARIS]
Is that a friend of yours?
[AMADEUS]
I'm not even human, actually.
I'm artificial intelligence.
An AI that Maho helped develop.
Huh?
Yeah, AI. Not aye-aye.
For real?
Actual artificial intelligence?
[DARU gasps]
Huh?
[AMADEUS]
Hi, everyone.
I assume you're the other
members of Okabe's laboratory.
Please allow me to
introduce myself.
I am called Amadeus.
I am a program of
artificial intelligence
constructed from the
memories of Makise Kurisu.
Makise Kurisu, huh?
[AMADEUS]
Ah, of course.
You must have been acquaintances
of the original me.
Uh, well, I wasn't, actually.
I only knew about you from
your articles in Sciency .
[AMADEUS]
Huh! I'm impressed.
If you were reading
that magazine,
then you must have
some level of interest
in advanced sciences.
Uh, well, I work with
systems and networks,
which straddle the divide
between science and math.
--[AMADEUS] Yeah?
--[NAE] Hey, miss AI lady?
Are you, like, a computer game?
Can I play online?
[AMADEUS chuckles]
No, I'm not a game.
I'm real. I'm right here...
[MAHO]
I'm sorry.
It seems cruel to say
you should let her go,
then put her right in your face.
I didn't intend to.
No.
It's probably better this way.
[MAHO gasps]
It's painful,
but I must keep moving
forward regardless.
As for Kagari,
she might resemble
Kurisu in some ways,
but she isn't her at all.
Same with Amadeus.
It was created from parts of
Kurisu, that's indisputable,
but it's a separate entity.
I can't let my grief
drag me down.
That's what you've wanted to say
this whole time, isn't it, Maho?
[OKABE]
That's right.
Kurisu protected this world,
along with Mayuri and
everyone else in it.
For her sake, I have to
keep protecting it...
...without ever looking back.
I don't think
Suzuha understands.
She still thinks
this world isn't right.
But now that Kagari is here,
even if she doesn't
remember anything...
...maybe that'll change.
Oh, by the way,
is Okabe there with you--
[ALL]
Huh?
What's wrong?
[DARU]
It cut out all of a sudden.
Let me see.
[MAHO] Hmm. My phone seems
to be working just fine...
...but I can't connect
to the Amadeus server.
--[gasps]
--That's weird.
That's never happened before.
[MAYURI]
Oh, no! I just wound you!
Don't tell me you're broken.
So not fair!
I've taken extra good care
of you and everything.
[MAYURI]
Hmm?
Do you think the server
could be updating or what?
If so, no one thought
to tell me about it.
[gasps]
Okabe, someone's coming!
[OKABE gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[MAHO]
What's going on?
Is this a prank?
[MAN 06A]
Nobody move!
[OKABE]
What is this?
Okarin?
[OKABE]
Not again.
Please.