[computer beeping]
[sighs]
[DARU]
Hey, Suzuha!
[SUZUHA]
Hm?
[DARU]
My lovely daughter!
You in there?
[SUZUHA]
What is up with all this,
"my lovely daughter" stuff, Dad?
That's what dads say to show
their daughters they love 'em.
[SUZUHA] I get that, but why are
you being overly sweet to me?
What's wrong?
You having problems in there?
You can't ask me that!
I have told you before,
if you have too much
information,
it could lead to a paradox.
On that note.
You could take this
hard drive back.
Oh, damn. You found it.
Of course, and you could've
hidden it a lot better
if you tried.
Probably.
Look, without her hard drive,
I don't know if I can
actually figure out
how to build this thing
in the future.
[SUZUHA]
No cheating allowed!
You could do it.
If you couldn't,
I wouldn't have been
able to come here.
You're going?
I am.
Okey dokey.
[SUZUHA] Main reason is because
I'm too happy and comfortable
living in this point in time.
Makes me want to
stay here forever,
and I know that's out
of the question.
I find myself
daydreaming about it.
[door opens]
Who's there?
Ah, Mayushii? What's up?
Suzuha?
[SUZUHA]
What?
Did something happen?
You came to us from way
in the future, didn't you?
It seems like everyone but me
knows the whole story.
[SUZUHA]
Listen, Mayushii--
I want you to tell
me about myself,
and about Makise Kurisu.
[BOTH gasp]
[train rumbling]
Hope you like Okinawa tea.
Where did Daru go?
We ran out of snacks,
so he went to pick up some more.
Well, that's good, right?
Talks like this are
usually better
when fewer people are involved.
Does that mean you're
gonna be here for it?
[MAHO] Yeah. I'm a
scientist, after all.
I might be able
to provide support
in the form of information.
So,
Maho, you know what's going on?
Only a rough outline,
based on what the three
of them have told me.
Before we begin,
I need to ask you...
Why do you want to know about
this right now, all of a sudden?
Well, because...
Before this, I was afraid
of knowing too much
about the future.
But now...
[SUZUHA]
Now, what?
I ran into Okarin
yesterday evening,
and he told me... not to
think about any of this.
That it was all okay.
And yet, when he said it,
he just seemed so miserable.
Like he has for the past year.
Sad and gloomy.
I know what you mean.
Look, the thing is, knowing this
might not make any difference.
Uncle Okarin's a bit lost.
I understand, but
I still want to hear it.
If I never open up
to the whole truth,
I know that I'll regret
it someday.
All right, but look.
Uncle Okarin's the only one
who can carry memories
over from other world lines.
So, at best, I'm just piecing
together the story
from everything
he's relayed to me.
Tell me, did Makise Kurisu...
Did she sacrifice her life?
Did she choose to die
in this world line
just so that I could live?
I don't think you can call
what she did a sacrifice,
at least, not literally.
But it is clear that there are
at least two world lines.
In what we call the
"alpha world lines,"
Makise Kurisu lives,
and you die,
sadly.
But then, in the
"beta world lines,"
Makise Kurisu loses her life,
and you continue living.
So, that means the world
we're in here and now
is one of the beta world
lines, if that makes sense.
But could there be more?
Are those two world lines
the only ones that you know of?
I'm... not sure.
But I'd like to believe
there are more.
The Steins Gate
world line exists.
I'm fairly certain of that much.
But what is Steins Gate?
A world where both you
and Kurisu get to live,
and World War Three,
which supposedly begins
because of the time machine,
never even happens.
[SUZUHA] Dad told me
about it in the future.
It's the unknown world line
that we're trying to reach.
Uncle Okarin chose to live the
same awful summer over and over,
because he thought
he could find Steins Gate.
He truly believed that he could
save both you and Kurisu.
But no such luck.
So, all of Okarin's
suffering began
because I stopped him that day.
It is not your fault, Mayushii.
And to be honest, he was
already an absolute wreck
long before that.
He has the ability to remember
all the world lines
he experiences.
We call it Reading Steiner.
As a result of this,
he retains memories
about all kinds of people
across many world lines.
The feelings those people
tried to hide,
the things they never achieved
but wanted to,
and his fear of suddenly
losing those he loves.
Carrying all that around
is more than enough
to do significant damage
to a person's psyche.
Which is why I'm grateful
that you stopped him.
It might have been
a whole lot worse.
Yeah, but if I hadn't stopped
him, he would have gone back.
And he might be--
Okarin.
[SUZUHA] You look just like
your future self did--
or, will, I guess.
You'll stare up at the sky
with that same face and say,
"That day, if my Hikoboshi
had burned bright
just once more, it might have
changed everything for us."
[DARU]
Sorry to keep ya waitin'!
You sure took your time.
Where did you go, America?
Well, I splurged a little bit.
Ginza, baby!
What's the occasion?
Is it someone's birthday?
[DARU]
It's a farewell gift.
Farewell?
[DARU]
Check it.
I got the shortcakes that
you love so much, Suzuha.
And I got you two
because you're so sweet.
Jeez! You make me sound
like I'm five years old!
But what did you mean
by farewell?
Oh.
I made the decision to leave.
If I keep messin' around,
I'm gonna miss my window
to reach July 28th of last year,
which is the day that
Makise Kurisu died.
That's so sad.
And you don't have enough fuel
to travel back here, do you?
Think you'll succeed?
I don't know.
That's why I wanted you two to
get the time leap machine ready.
To try again that way,
in case I fail.
Suzuha.
You're going back to the past?
What will you do
when you get there?
Well...
I can't say, but I'm positive
that I won't be returning.
World line convergence
might mean that an irregularity
like me gets straightened
out in the mix.
"Straightened out,"
what do you mean?
[MAYURI]
Suzuha! Wait!
You can't go!
Please, stop!
Don't do this! Daru, please!
Love ya, kid.
Give 'em hell, okay?
Okey-dokey!
And, Dad?
Thanks for the cake.
Don't let her.
[SUZUHA]
Right.
The mission is now a go!
Are you really okay with this?
You can't be.
You're her father.
You've got to be at least
a little sad.
It just doesn't feel right!
You have to go stop her, Daru!
[DARU]
I won't.
I can't stop her.
[phone chimes]
Okarin?
Hey, Mayuri?
[MAYURI]
Hello? You there?
It's Suzuha, she's in
some major trouble!
Suzuha?
[MAYURI]
Yeah!
She's heading to get into
the time machine
and travel one year
into the past!
She's leaving, and she says
she can't come back!
You didn't listen.
Huh?
[OKABE] Why did you have to go
and talk to them about all this?
You tried to find out,
when I plainly told you not to!
It was better
when you didn't know.
The time we have i--
[electrical short]
Huh? Huh...
[MAHO]
What's the matter?
[DARU]
This whole past year...
There's something I've
constantly been asking myself.
Twenty-five years from now,
why do I do it?
Why do I decide to send Suzuha
back in time to this era?
[DARU] I think I may have just
wanted her to experience it.
Life in this world.
That's what helped me make up
my mind to let her go now.
I'll finish my duty, like Suzuha
set out to finish hers.
I swear I'll do the things
only I can do.
[MAHO]
What do you mean by that?
Well, 25 years from now,
your boy Daru
will create humanity's
very first operational
time machine!
What about me?
I don't know what to do.
I want to help, but I'm not good
enough at anything that matters.
[DARU]
You're the one who got Okarin
back on his feet, Mayushii.
What, you don't think
that's enough?
[MAYURI]
But that day,
If my Hikoboshi had come back
to life right then and there,
it might have changed
everything, and for the better.
You don't know.
My Hikoboshi's been empty
and miserable.
For this entire year,
he's seemed lonely.
Ever since I stopped him,
he's been missing
a part of himself,
and all I want
is for him to find it.
I only want Okarin
to be happy again!
I want it so bad
that I could cry!
I wish it so hard
I want to scream!
Because I...
I love Okarin, deeply.
Maybe just as much
as Kurisu did.
No, that's wrong.
I love him more.
Much more intensely
than Kurisu ever could have!
I have no doubt!
Still...
I don't care!
I love Hououin Kyouma
even more than Okarin!
When I felt like just
disappearing forever,
Kyouma's the one
who convinced me
that my life
was worth living.
All I want-- [sobs]
is to see Hououin Kyouma
return to me!
I'm desperate to hear
his arrogant,
maniacal laughter again!
I want that even if it means
I can never be his Orihime.
Even then.
There will only ever be
one Hikoboshi for me!
And that person is
Okabe Rintaro, no one else!
[DARU]
Well, in that case.
If that's how you really feel,
deep down,
then you know what
you've gotta do Mayuri.
Yeah.
So, Daru and Maho...
...it might just be for today,
but I'm going to stop
being his hostage.
[CROWD chattering]
[OKABE panting]
[OKABE]
What's going on?
I can't even get a signal.
Today is double-sevens day!
Come see Orihime in
a cute miniskirt!
Mayuri!
Okabe?
Daru, where did Mayuri go?
What?
Oh, well, she--
I can't get service anywhere!
Do you know why?
I've been looking into it,
but all I can seem to find out
is that there's
a disruption in Akihabara
that hasn't been repaired yet.
[OKABE]
The internet is working, right?
Um, yeah.
But it's weird, someone must
be covering up the outage,
'cause none of the sites
are even talking about it.
I logged onto @channel to see
if anything pinged
on the message boards,
but I think the occult
board might've gotten hacked.
Someone hacked it?
What is this post about?
"It appears that we,
the pair of twins,
will be temporarily driven away
from the place where we belong."
"Our Father and God
has at last discovered
how to unveil
our most sacred domains.
Thus, we may tell Father the
secrets of manipulating time,
and where to find them."
What the hell does that mean?
"Father and God"?
That's right. And look!
[MAHO] "So, please convey
this sacred message to the one
whom I respect the most.
I have always considered myself
to be characteristically
mediocre, unlike yourself.
However, you were the one
person I strove to emulate,
above all others.
I believe,
you are the one true Amadeus."
So, any idea who did this?
I know who did.
Amadeus Kurisu wrote
every bit of this post.
For real?
I need you to try to get through
to Amadeus right now.
Yeah, sure.
[gasps]
What does this mean?
Something wrong?
All of Amadeus' data
has disappeared!
"Driven away from
the place where we belong."
Just like she said.
Then, "the secrets
of manipulating time
and where to find them,"
was talking about...
[gasps] It can't be.
Kurisu's memories?
Impossible!
How could anybody have broken
through the firewall
protections on Amadeus'
deep memory data?
Wait! I hope that
I'm wrong, but guys,
do you think this means
someone out there knows
about the time
machine's existence now?
No. No way.
What, Daru?
Talk to us!
Okarin!
[OKABE]
Mayuri and Suzuha both?
Suzuha went back to try
and change the future alone.
And Mayushii...
She ran out after her.
[OKABE]
Mayuri!
Is it hopeless?
As long as that time
machine exists,
will it just continue to happen?
Let's get back to work, then.
C-2-0-3.
Suzuha!
Don't try to stop me.
I have to go.
No, I won't.
'Cause I want to come with you.
Back to the past.
To August 21st of last year.
Why August?
Because,
that's the day you
and Okarin time traveled.
I want to go to right
after that.
Another time won't work.
It'd be pointless.
And you're totally confident
about this?
[MAYURI]
Mm.
We won't ever be able to return.
Are you okay with that?
I can't pretend anymore that
my Hikoboshi never found me.
I can't pretend not to know
that the future me is filled
with nothing but regret.
All right, then.
Mayuri!
--[MAYURI gasps]
--[OKABE panting]
Where do you think you're going?
What do you think you're doing?
Why has it come down to this?
When I had started
to come to terms
with the way everything ended?
Tell me!
Why has it come to this?!
If you come any closer,
I will shoot.
Mayuri, you don't have
to do this, you know that!
Please don't ruin it, I beg you!
If you do,
every single sacrifice
that we've made
will have been for nothing!
[gasps]
If you go through with this,
Kurisu's death
will have been in vain!
Please don't!
I can't let you do that!
[groans]
--Okarin!
--He's fine.
The bullet just grazed him.
[OKABE]
I can't, and I won't.
Not again.
Okarin.
[OKABE]
I won't let you.
I refuse!
It doesn't matter!
It's pointless.
There are some things
that we can't just
pretend never happened.
Mayuri, no.
Even when it rains, it isn't
as if the stars stop existing,
you know?
Above the dark clouds,
they're still up there shining.
That's why I'm doing this.
I have to push away
the bad weather
that's been covering up
your brightness.
I'm begging you...
Be patient.
[OKABE]
Mayuri.
Mayuri!
[SUZUHA]
Are you sure about this?
I'm sorry.
The bleeding has stopped,
so I think you're gonna live.
What do you intend
to achieve there?
[SUZUHA]
I've told you time and again.
I'll finish my mission.
That means,
doing whatever it takes
to change the future
for all the people I love.
Though I do have my
doubts it will work.
So, Uncle Okarin.
This is goodbye.
[phone vibrates]
What does Dad want?
A D-mail from the future?
What the--
Uh--
[DARU]
Yo, Suzuha. It's your dad.
Reaching out from
the year 2025.
Whoa, holy crap.
[DARU] If this video message
actually happens
to find you, well, congrats.
Because it means that you
and Mayushii have discovered
an alternative path
to reaching Steins Gate,
and I applaud you.
You may not even be
aware of it yet,
but the choice
the two of you made,
it altered the world line
ever so slightly.
Altered the world line?
[DARU]
In other words,
I'm not from the world line
you initially left.
Rather, I am a Hashida Itaru
from a different plane.
However, my love
for my daughter persists,
regardless of
the world line I'm in.
Now, moving on to the reason
I sent this message.
I must give you
detailed instructions
for Operation Arclight.
[MAYURI screams]
Let her go now!
[SOLDIER A] Put down your weapon
and get on the ground!
[MAYURI]
Suzuha!
[SUZUHA]
Mayuri, keep quiet.
If you scream, they won't
hesitate to shoot you.
[SUZUHA grunts]
Hey, I'm a woman,
in case you didn't notice.
Watch where you put
your filthy mitts.
[SOLDIER B] Targets two and
three have been secured.
[SOLDIER C]
Target one secured, as well.
Problem, though: there's
a lock on the device.
[SOLDIER A]
Biometrics, then?
[SOLDIER B]
Get up.
Yeah, fine.
Suzuha.
[SOLDIER B] If you try anything
funny, I'll shoot.
Yeah, I know.
[machine powering up]
[SOLDIER B]
Great, it's on.
We're good.
[yells]
[SUZUHA]
Mayuri! You have to run!
Mayuri.
What?
Kagari?