[MAHO]
For cryin' out loud.
You know, after that
New Year's Thief fiasco,
I had hoped things would
settle down, but nope.
--[door opens]
--Hm?
[laughs] Freeze, Maho!
This is a stickup!
What the heck did
you buy this time?
Isn't it wonderful?
I saw it in an Akihabara toy
store and couldn't resist.
It's an air gun.
I got it for the festival.
It's great! Shoots
beans in rapid fire!
So let's cast out the demons
and rake in the bucks!
Isn't that how it goes?
It's "bring in the
luck," Professor.
Besides, shouldn't
we be getting ready
for the trip back to America?
Stop buying junk, or we're
gonna run out of room.
And Reyes won't like you
leaving clutter here.
You're right, we did
borrow this office space.
We should be good guests
and leave it cleaner
than we found it.
But still, there'll be
plenty of time later
for packing up and cleaning.
For now, let's have fun.
It'd behoove us to check out
the festivals before we go home
and let loose in the
Japanese tradition!
Haven't you heard
the old saying, Maho?
When the cat's away,
the mice will play,
and I know the perfect time.
Setsubun! [laughs]
Setsubun, huh?
I can't believe it's
already that time of year.
Huh?
Almost Valentine's Day!
[SUZUHA]
See ya later, Boss.
Have a good night.
Guess we'll see you
in the morning.
[BRAUN]
Oh, hold on a sec.
[SUZUHA, KAGARI]
Hm?
[BRAUN] Here are your
wages for last month.
But... you're helping me out.
You protect me, so I work here.
I thought...
I pay my workers.
I have morals, you know.
[KAGARI]
But, sir.
[SUZUHA]
Come on, just take it.
Uh--
It's probably not very
much dough, anyway.
[BRAUN]
Oh, yeah?
[SUZUHA chuckles]
Sounds to me like somebody would
prefer to work for nothing!
Whoopsie, too slow!
Thanks for everything, Boss!
Why, you little...
Here you go.
[KAGARI]
Huh?
I really appreciate this!
[KAGARI giggles]
You sure seem happier
than usual today.
'Cause I am.
I've never been paid
for my work before.
Well, do you have any idea
how you're going to spend it?
[KAGARI] Hmm. That's
a really good question.
I'll have to give
it some thought.
[SUZUHA gasps]
Wanna go? This place has
the most delicious desserts.
[SUZUHA] Uh, no, that okay.
I was just curious, is all.
[SUZUHA]
What's up, Kagari?
Well, uh...
This poster...
What's it talking about?
[KAGARI]
Valentine's Day?
Yeah. It's a special day where
people show their affection.
Usually by giving the ones that
they love thoughtful gifts,
like chocolate.
Oh, I see. How nice.
[SUZUHA]
Back when I was a little girl,
my mom would search high
and low for the ingredients
to make us chocolates
for Valentine's Day.
[KAGARI]
How wonderful!
[gasps]
Showing your feelings
with candy?
That's such a remarkable custom!
I've decided I want to
participate in the tradition!
What? You do?
[RUKA] Hey, uh, do you
think that Kagari...
...might have a special
someone in mind here?
Huh?
[AMADEUS]
So?
You've got something
planned for him, right?
Are you ever gonna
give this thing up?
I've told you repeatedly,
not happening.
Do not crush my dreams!
You're going back
to America soon.
You have to tell him how you
feel before it's time to leave.
Will you stop?
For the hundredth time,
it's not like that!
If you convince yourself that's
the truth, you'll regret it.
I just think it's
better to take a chance
and make someone feel special,
even if it's "not like that."
Huh?
Maho?
[AMADEUS, MAKISE]
You there?
Ma'am?
[MAHO gasps]
Do you really not like anyone?
Yes, I told you that, now
will you give it a rest?
[MAKISE grunts]
[sighs] Besides, this
is America, you know?
From what I've seen,
the guys here
typically do the gift
giving, not the girls.
[MAKISE] Yeah, but don't you
think it coming from a girl
makes the gesture
even more romantic?
Bucking tradition to
reveal your feelings!
[MAHO] We're scientists.
Romance is not our forte.
"To be a scientist is
to be hopelessly romantic
in the truest sense."
Haven't you ever
heard that saying?
No, who said it? Einstein?
Yours truly.
[MAHO chuckles] Okay then,
Shakespeare, who do you like?
You're a beautiful
genius whose theories
are sure to be published
before you're 20.
There's a horde of men who'd
kill to be your Valentine.
[BOTH chuckle]
Since I've been in college,
several guys have approached
me with romantic intentions.
But as soon as we start talking,
they run away like I'm
some alien life form.
[MAKISE] Why can't they
handle losing a simple,
friendly debate? It's pathetic.
And besides.
I already have a special someone
in mind for Valentine's Day.
Wha--?
--[MAKISE gasps]
--Oh, no!
[MAKISE]
Anyway, I just think it's better
to take a chance and
make someone feel special,
even if it's not like that.
[MAHO]
Jeez.
What's wrong with you?
You're spacing out.
[MAHO]
Oh, sorry, it's nothing.
Regardless, this conversation
is officially over.
Are you serious?
[MAHO]
Don't give me that.
I'm shutting down now.
[FARIS] I overheard what you
were talking about in there.
Nya ha, ha, ha.
To think that Maho has a super
special someone in her life.
Excuse me?
[FARIS] Now you can pour
all those tender feelings
into your chocolate.
Reach out to your beloved!
Hang on! You're
completely delusional!
I never said anything
about a "beloved"!
[FARIS]
Oh, but you forget
I possess the eye of
the sky-god Horus.
I see what's written
on your heart.
Why doesn't anyone
ever believe me?
[MOEKA]
Chocolate.
--Huh?
--Uh?
--Meow, meow, meow!
--[MAHO gasps]
[yawns] Good morning.
Whoa, Kiryu?
How long have you been
hiding underneath there?
This whole time.
So that means you
heard everything.
I'm giving chocolate.
[ALL]
Huh?
I have someone to
give chocolate to.
[ALL gasp]
[AMADEUS] Does this mean
what I think it means?
[FARIS]
I'm so proud of Moe-meow!
Are you really going to
reveal your feelings to them?
Well, this is quite a surprise.
Yeah. I can't imagine you
confessing anything,
let alone love.
[AMADEUS]
So who is it, then?
[MOEKA]
Secret.
[MAHO]
What?
Delicious.
[KAGARI] So, uh... It goes
together like this, then?
No, no. You've got
it turned around.
But how? What have I done?
[SUZUHA]
Kagari has someone she likes.
[BRAUN]
Hello, ladies!
[NAE] Oh! Hi, Dad,
I'm glad you're back!
Well, Nae, have you
been a good girl?
[NAE] Yup! Miss Kagari and I
have been doing fun crafts!
Oh, you were?
Did you have a nice time?
Hey, Dad, guess what?
You know what Miss Kagari did?
No! Quiet!
She is the clumsiest
person I have ever met!
Nae! Why would you tell
him mean things about me?
[NAE]
Because!
Nothing to be
embarrassed about.
It's not like I
didn't already know.
Hey, c'mon, not you, too!
[NAE, BRAUN laughing]
[SUZUHA]
It can't be!
Mister Braun! I think
I'm in love with you!
You can't be, it isn't right!
You musn't think of me as a man,
but as Nae's father and
your boss, nothing more!
But someday... You and I...
We could raise her together!
I could be a mother to her!
[BRAUN gasps]
Stupid.
There's no way that's
what's going on here.
What's your problem?
Oh, hi! Uh, nothing! [laughs]
I--I was just daydreaming.
Uh, I'm gonna go
clean up out front.
Okay, bye, see you later!
Good afternoon.
Yeah? Oh, Okabe, it's just you.
What's up?
You find a new lead about
those attackers or somethin'?
No, sorry.
It's nothing as
important as all that.
[KAGARI]
Hi, Okarin!
So what brings you
into the shop today?
[OKABE] Uh, just came to
see how things are going.
Uh--you mean you came
to check up on me?
Yeah. You're looking quite well.
I appreciate you going
out of your way to visit me.
You must be so cold!
[OKABE] No, I'm fine.
I'm also here on an errand.
I've come bearing a
message from Mayuri.
She says that you and
I should go together
to pick out a cell
phone for you.
[KAGARI]
She really said that?
[SUZUHA] What are those
two talking about?
[gasps] It can't be!
You seem chilled to the bone.
[OKABE]
I feel warm now.
Your cheeks are flushed.
I've never seen them so
ruddy before. You see?
[gasps] Your hands.
[KAGIRI gasps]
I'm so sorry!
--[OKABE] Kagari. It's fine.
--Your cheeks,
they looked so cold, I had to...
[SUZUHA]
Oh, please, no.
Anything but that.
If that's how this
whole thing turned out,
Mayuri would never forgive me!
She would hate me forever!
Help me!
I have no idea what I'm
supposed to do here!
[FARIS] Thanks for doing
me this favor, meow!
[MAYURI]
Don't mention it!
You know I'd do anything
for a good friend in need!
And if you're a friend
of Mayushii's,
then we automatically adopt you!
I'm so glad to hear it!
Besides, making costumes
is our favorite pastime!
[FUBUKI] By the way, are you
going fully handmade, Mayushii?
Yup!
'Cause I think the customers
will appreciate that.
They love when we put
our hearts into it!
C'mon!
You know I'm not talking
about the café costumes.
Chocolate.
You're gonna give Okarin
homemade chocolate, right?
Uhh, yeah!
But I have to say,
I've never been
a very good cook,
so we'll see how it turns out.
[FUBUKI]
Well, in that case,
you should wear this.
It's okay, Okarin.
I can be your
Valentine's dessert.
[MAYURI]
Too-too-roo.
So hot! [laughs]
Uh, Fubuki?
Sometimes you sound exactly
like Daru, you know?
--[KAEDE, MAYURI chuckle]
--[FUBUKI] I'm so ashamed.
But, Mayuri, if you put
your heart and soul
into your chocolate,
I have no doubt that Okarin
will love them, no matter what!
[MAYURI]
Mm... I'm not so sure.
[FARIS chuckles]
[KAEDE]
What, Faris?
Mew just leave the
chocolates to Faris!
As of this meow-ment,
Let the 36th round table meeting
of Valentine chocolate-
making commence!
Round table?
Did she just say meow-ment?
[FARIS]
In other words,
we'll all be helping each other
make handmade chocolate.
Amazing!
That means you've done
this 35 times before?
[MAHO]
No. That's impossible.
[SUZUHA] I know they
invited me here for this,
Still, it makes no sense.
I don't even have a Valentine.
I'm curious about Kagari, but
this whole thing is ridiculous.
I'm leaving.
Are mew sure about that?
If you go, it means no yummy
chocolates for you to taste
when we're done!
[SUZUHA] Those things don't
matter to me. You know that.
[FARIS] Yuki's on her
way over meow, too.
Well, if you insist, I'll stay!
Besides, chocolate
is calorie-dense,
which is valuable in
times of emergency.
I knew you would come around!
All right! Time to get busy
making those chocolates!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Hey. Who are you planning to
give your chocolates to, Nae?
My dad, of course!
Oh, really? Are you
sure you're not gonna
give 'em to some hunky
guy in your class?
No! Don't be ridiculous.
What about you, Kagari?
My chocolates?
Well, you see...
That's a secret.
Tch.
Aw, come on, Kagari,
you've at least gotta
give us a little hint!
[KAGARI giggles]
[FARIS]
It's going exactly as planned.
If we hand out these gorgeous
girls' handmade chocolates
to the May Queen customers
on Valentine's Day,
it'll be a feat of
marketing genius!
What are you doing meow?
Shh! Be quiet!
You're gonna screw me up!
[MAHO yells]
I failed again!
You don't have to be
perfectly precise, you know.
[MAHO] Baking is a series
of chemical reactions!
An exact science,
with a slim margin of error!
Hey, meow.
Smells like something's burning.
[FARIS screams]
Huh, I wonder how this
could have happened.
You can wonder later!
Right now, just
put out the fire!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
[FARIS groans, gasps]
[FARIS]
Meow what'd you do?
I think I...
broke your microwave.
Oh, no!
Don't you know you're
not supposed to put
foil in the microwave?
--[explosion]
--Meow?!
Uh-oh.
[FARIS screams]
[FARIS] Everybody just stop what
you're doing and listen to me!
You have to follow the recipe!
If you don't, then
bad things happen!
--[clattering]
--[FARIS screams]
[FARIS]
I don't get it.
I was under the impression that
most people of a certain age
would understand the
basic rules of cooking.
[sighs]
--[YUKI] Hello!
--[gasps]
We're so sorry. We had
the start time wrong.
Oh. My saviors!
Yuki-meow! Ruka-meow! [sobs]
[RUKA]
Are you okay?
Um, here you go.
I don't know if they
turned out all right,
but I tried my very best.
[DARU] Please. Don't worry
your pretty little head.
I have no doubt that they're
gonna taste delicious!
--[DARU'S 2D WAIFU 24A giggles]
--[OKABE] Hey, Daru.
I hate to interrupt you in
the middle of... that, but...
...must you speak to
the characters out loud
when you play these
ridiculous games?
[DARU giggles]
I'm sorry, my bad.
[OKABE sighs]
[OKABE]
It's so peaceful.
If only it could last forever.
[FUBUKI]
Ooh!
I get it now!
So, then, it's the
heat of the water
that melts down the chocolate.
Exactly right.
Direct heat will burn it.
[FUBUKI laughs]
We learned that the hard way.
[RUKA gasps]
Okay. Did I do that right?
Yes. You're doing
an excellent job!
[SUZUHA gasps]
Uh, thank you. Thanks.
[FARIS] Looks like things are
going smoothly over here.
I've never been so
exhausted in my life!
It's like I've been set
upon by Hypnos himself!
--[clattering]
--[MAYURI gasps]
[MAYURI]
I'm so sorry, Ruka!
It's fine.
No, it's not!
If we don't wash
that out right away,
it's gonna leave a
big, yucky stain!
Please, it's just a
shirt, don't worry.
No, she's right.
Anything with oil needs
to be dealt with swiftly.
But--this is all I brought.
What will I wear?
[FUBUKI, KAEDE chuckle]
[gasps, screams]
[MAYURI gasps]
Wow. That's just incredible.
Come on. Why do I
have to wear this?
It's just temporary,
while your clothes are drying.
But you look stunning!
Honestly, I've never seen
a prettier human in my life.
This is crazy.
I can't even
believe it. For real.
Stop it!
Please give me
something else to wear!
[BRAUN sighs]
Perfect.
[MAYURI]
Woohoo! We did it, guys!
[SUZUHA sighs]
[FUBUKI] They turned out well,
all things considered.
[KAEDE giggles]
All right, so,
do we need to store them in the
freezer until Valentine's Day?
No, not with chocolate.
They should keep just
fine in the fridge
until it's time to
hand them out.
And I'll write down the recipe
so you guys can make them
on your own in the future,
any time you feel like it.
Verdict?
Uh--delicious.
Faris? What's the matter?
You look pale.
My lifeforce has been drained.
I am but a shell.
[NAE]
I don't think so, missy!
[FARIS]
Meow?
The round table
meeting isn't over
until that kitchen sparkles
like new-fallen snow, got it?
[FARIS]
Meow?
[NAE]
Listen up!
I'm gonna work you girls
until you beg for mercy,
and then I'm gonna
work you some more,
so you'd better get ready!
Are you with me?
[ALL]
Miss Nae! Yes, ma'am! Miss Nae!
[NAE]
I can't hear you!
You'll answer me like women
before you stuff your
faces with chocolate!
[ALL]
Miss Nae! Yes, ma'am! Miss Nae!
Nae sure is something else, huh?
[KAGARI]
You're right about that.
She's hilarious.
What? For real?
Kagari has the hots for Okarin?
[SUZUHA]
Maybe.
Well that sure sounds like
a recipe for disaster.
I mean, Kagari is
Mayushii's daughter,
so she might as well be--
Man, this means
the lucky bastard
has mother and daughter
all to himself?!
Gross, Dad.
[DARU gasps]
Yeah. Okay, well, jokes aside,
Kagari's from the future,
and if she's got a crush on
someone from the past?
There's a very high probability
of that leading to a
time paradox somehow.
It could be... dangerous.
Hey, Kagari--
[KAGARI]
I feel so happy.
[gasps]
[KAGARI] Making chocolate and
laughing with everyone today
was so much fun.
I may not remember
my past, but still.
I know I've never had
such a great time before!
At least, that's what I believe.
That's lovely.
[KAGARI giggles]
I hope... that my Valentine
is gonna like their chocolate.
[CAT CAFÉ MAIDS chattering]
[CAT CAFÉ MAID 24A] We're all
wearing extra special costumes
that we made especially
for you, masters!
Aren't you happy that
it's Valentine's Day?
We hope you'll like our
extra special service!
Gorgeous, delicious,
homemade chocolates
made with pure, loving care
by the girls of May Queen!
[PATRONS gasping]
Here you go.
Thanks so much!
You don't know
how much this means!
[CAT CAFÉ MAID 24C giggles]
[ALL chattering]
[FARIS] Everyone's having
such a great time!
[FARIS] I'm glad we only
do this once every year.
There's no way I could
put myself through it
more than that. Meow...
[FARIS]
Oh, yeah.
I wonder.
Did all the others give
out their chocolates yet?
[OKABE] You found these with the
things that Kagari left behind?
That's odd.
[RUKA]
Yes.
And they weren't just
for you two, either.
She left me a batch,
and one for my father,
and even the owner
who lives below us.
And to think, she was so
looking forward to this day.
Well, I'm sure she'll come back
to us soon, don't you think?
[KAGARI]
I hope...
...that my Valentine is
gonna like their chocolate.
[SUZUHA]
Actually tastes pretty good.
Stupid.
[AMADEUS]
Hold on.
You came back to America without
even giving out your chocolate
that you made?
Unbelievable!
I mean, I get that you had to
leave before Valentine's Day,
but that's what the mail is for.
Or you could've
given it out early.
I did give it out.
[gasps] Just to
make sure I'm clear,
we're talking about
chocolate, right?
[MAHO]
That's right.
--[creaking]
--Hey!
Don't just walk away!
Gimme details!
What did they say?
Did they like it?
[MAHO]
Nothing. They weren't around.
I was a little late
delivering it to them.
Uh--I don't get it.
Hey. Don't go.
Ma'am!
[MAHO]
These are for me?
[MAKISE] I heard this is
a thing in Japan lately--
giving your
Valentine's chocolate
to a very special friend.
But I don't--
I have nothing for you!
That's okay.
There's always next year.
[MAHO]
Thank you.