Okabe, someone's coming!
[MAN 06A]
Nobody move!
[OKABE]
What is this?
Okarin?
[MAHO gasps]
What is... this?
A sick prank or something?
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[OKABE]
I knew it.
She's betrayed us again.
[OKABE]
Kiryu Moeka.
[gunshot]
[RUKA, FARIS gasp]
Oh, no.
[MAN 07A]
He said don't move!
[MAN 06A]
K-6205.
[MAN 07B]
Copy.
K-6205, securing now.
[KAGARI gasps]
Kagari!
[KAGARI gasps, whimpers]
No! Help me! Mayuri!
--Stop!
--Be quiet!
You can't fight back!
[gasps]
[KAGARI]
Stop it! Let me go, please!
[KAGARI sobs]
--[BRAUN] Hey.
--[MAN 07C] Huh?
[MAN 07C gasps, groans]
[BRAUN] I warned you guys
to keep quiet up here!
--[MAHO gasps]
--Daddy!
[DARU]
Mr. Braun!
[MAN 07D gasps]
[BRAUN grunts]
--[KAGARI gasps]
--Kagari!
[SUZUHA]
Stop!
Get back here!
[sighs]
[NAE gasps]
Oh, Daddy!
--[BRAUN chuckles]
--[NAE cries]
Everything's okay, sweetie.
Daddy's got you now. Don't cry.
[NAE crying]
[OKABE sighs]
[BRAUN] You've got some
explaining to do, Okabe.
Who the hell were those punks?
They were...
--[footsteps]
--[gasps]
[FUBUKI]
Hey, we're back!
Hi! We got more than enough
drinks for everyone.
[FUBUKI]
Hold up.
Why do you guys
all look terrified?
[FUBUKI gasps]
What happened to the TV?!
[KAEDE]
Be careful where you step.
Where's the broom and dust pan?
[OKABE] Mayuri and the other
girls got home safe, at least.
[DARU]
Good.
Maho made it back
to her office, too.
She said she's gonna sleep
at the institute tonight,
just in case.
That's smart.
Good call.
[DARU]
Hey, Okarin?
Huh?
Those people who broke in
were after Kagari, right?
Yeah.
[DARU]
I have a theory.
It seems to me like they know
Kagari is from the future
and that's why they want her.
[DARU]
Maybe...
...during the time
that she was missing,
some bad stuff happened to her.
I agree.
[OKABE]
SERN's Rounders.
In another world,
that same organization
attacked and captured us,
because we developed
a time machine.
[OKABE]
But, wait!
Even if this is a
different world line,
Tennoji would still be the boss
of all the Rounders
in Akihabara.
If he's the enemy,
it doesn't make sense
that he'd be helping us.
Which makes me think that the
woman in the motorcycle suit
wasn't Moeka Kiryu, at all.
But someone else.
I still can't believe any
of this actually happened.
Guys with guns? In Akiba?
You never hear 'bout
stuff like that in Japan.
It's starting to turn out
like Suzuha said.
[DARU] It almost feels like
we're in the bizarro world,
or one of those cheesy
American prank shows,
but, like, a twisted,
dystopian version.
[OKABE]
I know the feeling, buddy.
[DARU sighs]
[OKABE]
And yet, this is reality.
I can't deny it...
as much as I want to.
That same scene
I relived countless times.
The gun smoke,
the screams,
the blood...
[OKABE gags]
[DARU]
You okay?
[OKABE]
I'm fine.
Wanna take a break?
[OKABE]
No.
I hate to say it, but...
...this could all just be
the choice of Steins Gate,
or something.
Steins Gate.
What nonsense.
It's all beginning
to sound so pathetic.
Whoa, dude!
You can barely
even stay upright.
Let me help you out.
--[OKAABE] I'm fine!
--Here.
Come on. No shame in it.
Hey...
Is it gonna happen again?
That horror movie BS?
I'll make sure it doesn't.
I'm gonna find a way to stop it.
[FEMALE VOICE 07A] We're sorry.
You have reached a number
that has been disconnected,
or is no longer in service.
If you feel you have reached
this recording in error,
please check the number--
[sighs]
Where could the professor be?
And why'd he go AWOL
at a time like this?
[MAHO groans]
No matter what I try,
I can't connect to Amadeus.
What on earth is going on here?
[phone buzzing]
Hey, Dad, what's up?
[DARU]
Suzuha! Papa got worried.
How's it going?
[SUZUHA] The security
here is a lot beefier
than I imagined it would be.
Especially for a shrine.
I think Ruka's dad might be
one of those paranoid dudes.
I know they've had
some sort of system
in place for a while now.
They were having
problems with weirdos
trying to sneak in
at night, so...
What they've got is still
kind of over the top.
[DARU] Yeah, they might've asked
Okarin for help designing it,
and you can imagine
how that went down.
Also, I may have installed
a hidden camera or two.
Fascinating!
Well, we can rest assured.
This place might as
well be a fortress.
[DARU]
Awesome.
Just give your daddy a call
if anything crazy happens.
[SUZUHA]
Right.
You be careful out
there, okay, Dad?
You're not as strong
as I am, you know.
[DARU]
You can do better than that!
Say, "Papa, you're a worthless
normie pig who can't even--"
[door opens]
[gasps] I'm glad you're back!
How's Kagari?
[RUKA]
She was really shaken up.
She just fell asleep
a minute ago.
[SUZUHA]
I see.
You must be exhausted,
too, Ruka.
Get some rest.
Security-wise,
everything's under control.
I'll keep an eye out.
But, Suzuha...
You're not gonna sleep?
I'm not much of a sleeper.
I want to stay on alert,
in case anything happens.
[RUKA]
Seriously?
But you won't be able to
if you don't get some rest.
[SUZUHA]
That's okay.
I'm used to it.
[KAGARI]
Mommy...
Mommy, please don't leave me.
[KAGARI cries]
[KAGARI]
Mommy...
[RUKA]
El. Psy. Congree.
Hey, um... can I
ask you something?
[SUZUHA]
What is it?
[RUKA]
Well...
There've been instances,
when you've been
talking to Okabe,
that you've called
him "Uncle Okarin."
Why is that?
And you're so
familiar with Mayuri,
like you're best friends.
You're that way with Faris, too.
You act like you've
known her all your life,
but I know you haven't.
You treat me that way.
It's almost as if
we're your family.
[RUKA]
And then Kagari...
She was saying "Mommy"
just now, wasn't she?
I'm not sure, but I swear
that earlier, in her sleep,
I heard her say...
..."Mommy Mayuri."
That has to mean our
Mayuri, don't you think?
But why would she
call her Mommy?
[SUZUHA]
I'm sorry...
...but it's better
if you don't know.
[RUKA]
It always is.
Once again, everyone is
leaving me out the loop.
Okabe and Mayuri
always look so sad lately.
Hashida and Faris,
they all seem to be
bearing a huge burden.
I probably couldn't help.
I have no delusions
about who I am.
But even so...
...I care about them.
And not knowing makes
me feel so lonely!
I get it.
[RUKA]
Please tell me.
I'm begging you.
[SUZUHA] The thing
about Uncle Okarin is...
You're the only person
he refuses to tell,
and I think I understand
his reasons now.
[RUKA]
You do?
[SUZUHA]
He wants to protect you.
To save you from having to
know any world but this one.
So the only burden
you'll ever have to bear
is the world you exist in now.
Somehow, in Uncle Okarin's
mind, you're... his salvation.
I am?
[SUZUHA]
Yeah.
But... that's...
I don't even know
what to do with that.
Okabe...
You should try to
get some sleep.
Good night.
[BRAUN scoffs]
You decided to show up.
Well? What the hell
happened yesterday?
[OKABE]
Steady, now.
If my instincts are right,
it should all work out.
[BRAUN]
So, talk.
Did you come to explain
or just stand there?
[BRAUN slurps]
Look, before I talk,
I need confirmation.
You didn't have anything to do
with the incident, did you?
Huh? What is your problem?
Why the hell would I have
something to do with this?
[OKABE]
Isn't it obvious?
I've no idea what
you're on about.
If you don't quit jerking my
chain, I'll raise your rent.
I know who you are!
And what you are.
You, Mr. Ferdinand Braun,
you're the Rounder
known to his cohorts as FB.
[NAE]
What's wrong, Daddy?
[BRAUN]
Hmm?
[NAE]
You look scary all of a sudden.
I do? I'm no different
than usual, sweetie.
Now why don't you
go play outside?
Better yet, you can go
put on some headphones,
and watch anime
over there, okay?
And you can even turn
the volume all the way up!
Really? Awesome! [giggles]
[OKABE]
How telling.
You wouldn't want
little Nae to find out.
The woman in the motorcycle
suit whose men attacked us--
That wasn't your subordinate,
Moeka Kiryu, was it?
[BRAUN] It wasn't even
the Rounders at all.
It's someone else.
[BRAUN]
I have no choice but to ask you.
What proof do you
have of any of this?
[OKABE] You wouldn't
believe me if I told you.
[BRAUN]
Come on, kid, try me.
[gasps]
[BRAUN chuckles] That face of
yours says you came in here
ready to spill what you know.
[YUKI]
Oh, my gosh!
But why didn't you guys
call the police?
[FUBUKI]
Good question.
Okarin told us to
hold off on that.
You're kidding me!
'Cause, like, they had guns!
Anyway, he's got something
he wants to tell us.
[YUKI] You mean you're
going back to the lab?
It'd be pretty stupid for
them to strike there twice,
according to Hashida.
Makes sense.
Well, I wish I could come to
the lab and see what's up.
What happened to your arm?
[gasps]
I tripped over
myself! [chuckles]
So clumsy!
[YUKI chuckles]
[BRAUN] Time machines
and world lines, huh?
Probably don't need to say
this, but I gotta be honest:
it's hard to believe.
[OKABE] I know this is
redundant, but I told you so.
Yeah, you did. Still though.
Everything you said
about me is accurate.
You've caught my attention,
and your facts are so spot on,
it's creepin' me out.
I also know SERN's
secrets are confidential.
No question.
It doesn't matter if their
mission succeeds or fails,
the result is the same:
they eliminate anyone
who knows the truth.
Seems like you know everything.
In which case...
[OKABE] Listen.
None of this has anything to do
with your mission!
Your secrets were
never actually leaked!
I just happened to
know them from the start.
So that means there's no reason
for them to punish you!
[BRAUN]
How convenient.
But once again,
you're not wrong.
SERN hasn't said anything
about this to me yet.
So if you can keep it
quiet that I'm a Rounder,
we shouldn't have a problem.
Now, what do you want, exactly?
You wouldn't open up
without some ulterior motive.
What is it, kid?
I need to ask a favor of you.
Kagari Shiina.
They're after her and I
want you to protect her.
Tell me who's targeting her
and why, and I'll consider it.
I don't know.
Then I think we're done here.
Let's both just pretend
we never talked.
[OKABE]
You can't do this!
If those people from
yesterday come back...
...what would happen to Nae?
She could be put in
grave danger again.
[BRAUN]
You bastard.
You think you can
make Nae your hostage?
You want to die?
Wait! I'm just saying
we should work together.
If we do this alone,
then we're much more
vulnerable to their attacks!
[BRAUN] If I help you,
I'm risking everything
for no pay off!
[SUZUHA]
That's not quite true.
You'd stand to gain a lot.
You little...
You were listening?
[SUZUHA] If you let Kagari
and me work here part time,
it would make it easier.
It'd be way less work for you.
Evicting all of you
from the building
sounds like a much better plan.
That would keep Nae and me safe.
[SUZUHA] Remember: you and Nae
witnessed yesterday's attack.
They saw you.
So I don't even
need to tell you.
I think you already
know what that means.
[BRAUN grunts]
--[NAE] Daddy?
--[gasps]
Yesterday scared me.
I don't understand,
but I didn't like it.
I, uh...
But... thinking of you
getting hurt protecting me...
That scares me more than
anything else in the world.
So I think I'd feel safer with
Suzuha and Kagari here to help.
You would?
[BRAUN groans]
Just so we're clear,
you two will be splitting
one person's pay.
I'm not some damn
billionaire TV tycoon.
Yay!
[OKABE gasps]
Cheapskate, huh?
[sighs]
One more word and
I'll raise your rent!
No, sir, Mr. Tennoji. Thank you.
[BRAUN] Hmph. Well, then,
Okabe... get to work.
You better find out
who those bastards were.
If you don't...
...we can't do much
to protect your friend.
I understand.
[KAEDE] Do you think
that during the time
Kagari can't remember...
...she was mixed up in some
sort of crime or something?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
[FUBUKI]
So, again...
Why don't you just
go to the police?
[DARU] Well, you see,
she's afraid of cops.
And for all we know,
they could be involved somehow.
If they're connected
and we call them,
then we'd be giving
her to the enemy!
[FUBUKI] Wow. I don't know
if I buy what you're selling.
[OKABE]
Uh... Well, regardless.
They only seem to be
targeting Kagari,
but for the time being,
you should all steer clear of
this building, just to be safe.
What? No way!
[KAEDE]
And what about Kagari's safety?
Those people are
still after her!
We've got two bodyguards on her.
People we know we can trust.
If it's Suzuha and Mr. Braun,
then I feel better.
[OKABE]
And we're conducting our own
investigation, too, naturally.
We'll find out who they are
and what they want with Kagari.
Yep! The perfect job
for yours truly.
And Akiba's
neighborhood vigilantes
have promised to be out,
prowling the streets
night and day.
So if someone's up to no good,
they'll send up a signal, meow!
Um...
Is there anything I can do
to help the investigation?
Kagari is my friend
and she's in trouble.
I don't want to just sit around
doing nothing about it.
[MAYURI] Yeah, I want
to help Kagari, too!
Rukako, you're already
providing Kagari with shelter.
Mayuri, you've been
there for her
in a way no one else could be.
You've done enough.
[RUKA sighs]
What can the rest
of us do to help?
[OKABE]
K-6205.
What is that? Some sorta code?
Tennoji said something.
[BRAUN]
Now that I think about it,
I remember those guys
saying something weird.
What did they say?
Wasn't it... Yeah.
K-6205, or something like that.
The way he said it
was so distinct.
It's phonetic code.
What is phonetic code?
Used in the military.
Mostly in the western world.
[DARU]
Hmm.
So far, I'm only seeing it
in boring stuff
like product codes.
What about Kochel numbering?
Never heard of it.
It's a special numbering system
for Mozart's compositions.
But what am I thinking?
He didn't write 6,000 pieces,
so that couldn't be it.
[OKABE]
Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart.
[FARIS] What if it's not
6,205, but part five of 620?
Six-hundred and twenty?
I think that's Magic Flute .
[keyboard clacking]
Oh, wow. Nailed it.
It says, "This opera is famous
for it's Masonic elements,
as both Mozart and the
librettist were Freemasons,
and for its symbolism."
"Amadeus"?
[MAHO] I can't connect
to the Amadeus server.
That's weird.
[OKABE gasps]
Okarin?
[line ringing]
[MAHO]
Hi, this is Hiyajo.
Hello? It's me.
Oh, Okabe.
Did something happen?
[OKABE] No. I need
to ask you something.
Okay, just make it quick.
I'm kind of in the
middle of stuff.
It's about Amadeus.
Any luck?
[MAHO]
Nope.
I can't access it.
I shudder to think this, but...
...someone may have
hacked the server.
[OKABE gasps]
[MAHO]
I've gotta hang up now.
We can talk later.
Okarin?
[phone vibrates]
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
Amadeus.
[MAKISE]
Okabe. Can you hear me?
[BOTH gasp]
--[OKABE] Kurisu!
--[MAKISE] Please help me.
Are you there?
Okabe--
[OKABE grunts]
[OKABE]
Reading... Steiner?!
[gasps]
[OKABE]
Amadeus. It disappeared.
[OKABE] Could the
world line have changed?
But how?
[door opens]
[OKABE]
Someone's there.
But who?
Daru? Mayuri?
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
Kurisu?