[BRAUN growls]
Nothin' ever changes...
--[explosion]
--[BRAUN grunts]
What the--?!
Hey, what's going on up there?!
You trying to get evicted?!
[MAHO, DARU coughing]
[MAHO]
The window! Open the window!
[DARU]
Okey-dokey!
Didn't see that coming.
[MAHO] Why did it just
start spewing fire?
Not sure, but I bet
it has something to do
with finding it
atop a pile of trash.
That smoke is thick,
better turn on the AC.
[DARU] You can't! If we run
both that and the microwave,
it'll trip the breaker.
Man. No self-respecting
scientist
would ever call
this dump a lab.
Yeah, you're certainly
right about that part.
Okarin's the one who
came up with the name.
[MAHO]
To think that Kurisu
was able to put
this thing together
under such adverse conditions.
[rain pouring]
[PROFESSOR]
It can be confusing.
As you'll find in
the example on page 21,
direct versus indirect
speech depends on
whether you're
repeating or reporting--
[school bell rings]
We'll pick it back up
here next time.
[PROFESSOR]
Oh, one moment, Okabe.
Of course, Professor.
Ah, Okarin!
Hey, thanks for waiting.
Sure. So, your professor
wanted to have a chat with you?
That's right. Seems
like Viktor Chondria is
interested in Daru, as well.
They're eager to meet him.
[MAYURI]
Wow, really?
So awesome!
Ha, that's our smart,
super hacker for ya!
[OKABE]
Indeed.
You wanna grab a bite?
[MAYURI] Huh? You don't
wanna go to the lab?
I'm pretty sure Daru's there.
[OKABE]
I'll just send him a message.
[MAYURI] But I know it would
make him really happy
to hear it from you in person.
Anyway, so much
has happened lately
between him and Yuki, you know?
You wanna hear what I think?
Your best friend needs you
to be there for him.
Yeah, but next week is my--
[phone vibrates]
[MAYURI] You've got such
a normie life now, don't you?
[OKABE]
I wouldn't go quite that far.
But since I do
have the opportunity,
it would behoove me to
take it and study overseas.
[MAYURI]
I guess.
So, this is something
you really want to do, then?
It is.
[MAYURI] In that case,
I think you should go for it!
It might also be
a good thing for Daru.
Plus, if I end up transferring,
I'll be able to lend
a hand to Hiyajo
when she needs it.
Seems to be the best thing
for everyone.
Know what I mean?
Right. Almost forgot!
Look at this pic of Suzuha!
Don't you think
she looks so silly like this?
Yeah, like she's
wearing a bad costume.
Oh, and don't worry
about the lab coat.
She's just wearing your old one.
The new coat is still
stored away, safe and sound.
She could've worn it.
No big deal.
What?
But the last time I tried
to let Suzuha wear it,
you got super annoyed,
and you kinda
snapped at me.
[OKABE]
Did I really?
It's only a cheap lab coat.
Come on, it's green.
I'm sorry.
I just remembered something
I forgot to take care of.
All right, then.
[MAYURI]
Um, Okarin?
[OKABE]
What is it?
[MAYURI]
Nothing. Never mind.
I'll see you around!
[phone vibrates]
[MAYURI]
Please, stop it!
It isn't fair for you
to force him like this!
And why?
Why does Okarin
have to carry the weight
of the future all by himself?
[phone vibrates]
[RUKA] I'm sorry. I just
forgot my umbrella.
No, it's okay!
I happened to be out and
about when you called,
so it's perfect! [giggles]
We're sharing an umbrella
like a couple!
Stop it, you're embarrassing me!
[MAYURI]
Wow!
Look at that huge
Tanabata display!
[RUKA] Can't believe
it's that season already.
[MAYURI] I like to make
my own display every year!
I even buy a branch
of bamboo for it.
Oh, do you really?
And do you hang a wish from it,
and everything?
Yup!
The same one,
ever since I was little.
I've always wished
that I could
somehow become Orihime.
[chuckles] You know me.
I'm a totally delusional,
hopeless romantic at heart!
[RUKA]
You will be Orihime, I know it.
And Okabe will be
your Hikoboshi.
Huh? Hold on, now.
I don't remember
saying anything
about Okabe in all this!
[RUKA]
Yeah, but Mayuri,
you've stood by his side
for all this time.
You would be
perfect for the job.
[MAYURI]
You're wrong.
[gasps]
Okarin does hold someone
in that special place
in his heart, but it's not me.
[gasps]
And, do you know
the saddest part?
His Orihime
won't shine anymore.
'Cause she's gone now.
[RUKA]
Mayuri...
[MAYURI]
You're very kind, Ruka,
you know that?
[RUKA]
No, I'm really not.
It's just that this is
the only thing I know I can do
to help right now.
[DARU]
Damn this heat.
[MAHO]
Hey, in a few minutes,
I wanna try
the experiment again.
'Kay.
Also, if you attempt
to sneak a peek at me,
I'll call Suzuha so fast
your head'll spin.
[DARU] You don't need to worry
about that, Legal Loli.
I don't think my heart could
take it, not in this weather.
--[door clangs]
--[DARU gasps]
[OKABE]
Huh? Hey, Daru!
Oh, no, it's Okarin!
Okabe's here? Crap!
[DARU stammering]
[DARU]
Oh, no!
Hey, Daru! Mayuri?
Someone's in there!
[DARU] Uh, yeah, just
hold on a second, 'kay?
[BOTH grunting]
Come on in!
Hentai games again?
[DARU]
Heh. No. Uh, I mean, yeah.
I was just cleaning things up
when you tried the door.
[OKABE]
Spare me the foul details.
Smells like smoke in here.
[DARU]
Uh, I was heating up a bento
when this crappy
microwave I just got
decided to blow up on me!
It blew up?
We're gonna get evicted
if you're not careful!
[DARU chuckles nervously]
So, anyway, what brings
you down to the lab?
Mayushii's not here right now.
[OKABE]
Yeah, well, Kiryu got some intel
that said Kagari,
or someone who looks like her,
was seen in the area recently.
You heard anything?
Um, nope. Nothing at all.
Can I use the PC?
[DARU]
Uh, wait, just, gimme a sec.
All yours.
[OKABE] I'm sure you weren't
doing anything illegal.
Oh, I've got some
good news for you.
GTFO!
I haven't even
said anything yet!
Yesterday, I was having lunch
with Professor Leskinen.
He was telling me--
Dude, is this about
going overseas?
[OKABE]
Just let me finish, would you?
He was telling me that
he's interested in your work,
as are his colleagues.
Viktor Chondria has a renowned
computer science department,
and they seem
to want you in it.
Yeah, sounds cool.
[OKABE] And with skills
like yours, you can get by.
I'm a super hacker,
for crying out loud,
I would do more than
just "get by," dude.
You don't want to?
It's not that I don't want to,
it's just that given
the current situation,
most of my focus is
somewhere else these days.
What with Suzuha
wanting to go back
to the past and everything.
[gasps]
[MAHO grunting]
Anything fun going on
with the old @channel?
Not quite.
Nothing I would deem "fun,"
but perhaps intriguing.
Rumors about that
facility in Chiba.
On the occult board? I bet.
Those idiots just sit around
all day long
dreaming up their bullshit.
Don't believe anything
you read on there.
[OKABE]
That username is...
--[thud]
--[DARU groans]
[DARU gasping]
[MAHO]
You idiot!
[OKABE]
Is that a bunch of bananas?
No, I mean, yes,
but it's not what you think.
Suzuha put me on this
silly all-banana thing
to help me slim down.
That seems peculiar.
[gasps]
Hold on, Okarin!
Hear me out.
[OKABE]
That takes me back.
Mayuri used to get so angry.
She'd scold us for wasting
perfectly good food.
Yeah, I remember.
[trash rustling]
[gasps]
Explain this to me.
What is this?!
Well, I guess the cat's
outta the bag.
So much for trying
to keep it under wraps
while we figured things out.
It's the Phone-Wave,
real name TBA, unit 02.
[OKABE] You actually did it.
You rebuilt it?
[DARU] I wasn't sure
whether to call it
version two or unit 0--
[OKABE] Who gives a shit
about the name?!
Really? Man, that doesn't
seem like you at all, Okarin.
You made a huge deal
about the nomenclature
of the Future Gadget Lab,
and the Roundtables--
[OKABE]
You remember that, huh?
Well, did you forget
everything else?!
That thing shouldn't exist!
Don't you understand
all that's at stake?
Relax! What I haven't
forgotten is, eventually,
we have to build a fully
functioning time machine,
and I figure we gotta
finish working on this
as the precursor to that.
Daru!
I have explained all this
to you ad nauseum!
You know what this wretched
thing is responsible for!
You understand
everything I went through
because of it, don't you?!
Because we created it,
Mayuri gets killed
over and over again.
Because we built this thing,
Kurisu's life
must be sacrificed.
Because we did this,
your own daughter kills herself!
All this death because
we created a monster!
[DARU]
Okarin...
If you don't remember,
I will tell you every detail.
I won't stop till the images
are burned into your brain!
'Cause it seems like
you won't fully grasp it
until you've gone through
the pain of it all, like I did!
You idiot!
[MAHO]
Okabe Rintaro, stop this!
You're the idiot!
[OKABE]
Hiyajo?
Wait, what are you doing here?
[gasps] Well, I, uh...
I just stopped by on impulse.
On impulse, huh?
[gasping]
[DARU grunts]
Legal Loli for the win!
Take one look,
and I'll sue you!
Sorry to make you guys wait.
So to sum up,
you're saying you were hiding
from me this whole time?
[MAHO]
That's right.
And is this work why
you came back to Japan?
[MAHO]
Yes. The real reason I'm here
is to help Daru develop
the terribly named
Phone Wave, real
name TBA, unit 02.
Don't get mad at him.
He wasn't the one
who asked me to come back.
Thanks, Maho.
He is the one who initially
got into contact with me,
but he was only doing it
because Suzuha made him.
[OKABE]
Suzuha?
[DARU]
Yeah, and she was desperate.
She needed Maho to help me
'cause the time machine's
low on fuel.
There's only enough
to jump back one year.
[DARU] It isn't long
until the anniversary
of Miss Makise's death.
After that passes,
we won't be able to go back
and change
the world line branch.
That's why.
If we fail and have
to try again,
then the only option
will be the time leap machine.
[OKABE]
So, you dragged Hiyajo into it.
[DARU]
At first, I hoped
I could leave
everyone else out of things
and figure it out by myself.
But in the end,
I was stumped.
[OKABE]
And you?
You admit to helping him
betray me like this?
Yes, I do,
and with no regrets.
[OKABE]
But why?
I explained
the situation to you!
I told you what the D-mails
brought about!
You should understand
the dire consequences
of changing the past!
And yet you were willing
to risk that happening?!
Don't you get
what this could mean?!
If you go back
and change the past,
you bear the responsibility
of taking another person's life!
And that person
is your friend, Mayuri!
--You would kill her!
--Stop it! I'd never do that!
[OKABE] Saving Kurisu's life
equals Mayuri's death!
There's no avoiding it.
No matter how hard
you try to save her,
she ends up dead.
Your attempt to build
a time leap machine
tells me you're trying
to change the past.
And if you succeeded,
that would mean Kurisu's
sacrifice would be in vain,
and we'd go right back
to the alpha world line!
You would be
killing off Mayuri again!
Do you really want to have
her murder on your conscience?
[DARU]
Okarin!
[DARU grunts]
Apologize!
Apologize to Maho
right now, dammit!
[MAHO]
What the--?
[DARU] I get where you're
coming from, Okarin,
and I understand
that you're still grieving.
I can't even begin
to imagine the suffering
you've been through, but still!
That doesn't
give you the right
to shit all over
everyone else's feelings
like you're the only one
who matters!
[MAHO]
That's enough, c'mon!
No, it's not.
Suzuha traveled here
to stop World War Three
from happening.
Maho cared so much
about Miss Makise
that she dropped everything
and came to help me
build the time leap
machine, man!
You think we're doing
all this just to betray you?
And Mayushii's no different!
You have no idea
what she's experienced,
and it's all for your sake.
Seriously, give it a rest!
Just take a few deep breaths.
Okay?
[OKABE]
Daru... just hit me...
[MAHO]
Serves you right,
for all the dumb
things you said.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean
a lot of that stuff.
Yeah, I know you didn't.
Gotta say,
I like you better now.
I'm glad to see you lose your
cool like a normal person.
He's usually so gentle.
Non-violent. Makes it worse.
Just so we're clear,
we were only trying
to build the machine.
There was no discussion
of going further than that.
We had zero intention
of sending any D-mails.
Yeah, I'm sure.
[MAHO] And yet, you still
look disappointed.
[OKABE]
Well, it stopped raining.
Let's go get some fresh air.
[MAHO]
What's wrong?
Nothing.
[OKABE]
The way I see it...
My world only exists
because of a choice Kurisu made.
Because of Kurisu,
Mayuri can live
her whole life.
I must protect
that choice at all costs.
It's the law
governing this world.
[MAHO]
Yeah, but you wrote it.
[OKABE] In reliving time,
I learned one thing.
That certain events are fixed,
as if orchestrated
by the divine.
And to try
and change said events
is a challenge to the gods.
And one thing they won't abide
is Human arrogance.
Maybe so.
I may be a proud scientist,
but my plans don't include
invoking celestial wrath.
But you might.
Hold on. I think you're wrong.
I don't think
this has much to do
with gods
or laws of this world.
Hiyajo, listen--
[MAHO] If there is a single
set of concrete laws
governing everything,
and if all things
are set in stone
that way by the divine,
fating us to a static path,
then there's no point
in having free will
at all, is there?
[OKABE] I'm not saying
everything is preordained,
just that certain
fixed points can't be changed!
[MAHO]
Then what are those?
Tell me what can't be changed
by the laws of this world,
and what's fair game,
since you claim to know.
I don't know.
[MAHO] Any scientist worth
his salt would ask that.
The way I see it,
the laws you describe
are more like a formula.
They're just another set
of circumstances to unlock,
like a combination.
And I believe
we can figure it out.
People have wills.
They use their minds
to make decisions
and take action.
That's what makes
the world what it is.
Solving this
may not be an easy feat,
but if we work hard,
and most importantly
if we work together,
we can figure it out!
But going back in time
is too dangerous to--
Let's reach Steins Gate.
I thought long and hard
about what Suzuha told me.
Mayuri lives,
Kurisu lives,
and World War Three is avoided,
sparing billions
of lives worldwide.
If that's what you
refer to as Steins Gate,
then we have our formula.
We know that value, at least,
and we just need to solve
for the other missing pieces.
I don't know what to say.
[MAHO] This world is full
of infinite possibilities.
And the solution
is somewhere among them.
So, let's find it!
Let's look and keep looking!
A thousand times, or a million,
if that's what it takes!
Find a solution
to Steins Gate!
Like you and Kurisu tried,
together!
[OKABE gasps]
--[OKABE] But I can't!
--Please, Okabe!
[OKABE]
It's easy for you to stand there
and spew those words,
but you don't understand
how it rips my heart to shreds!
You don't know the toll it
takes, failing over and over!
But I do know!
You have no idea!
Yes, I do! I lived it,
and Kurisu was right there,
failing thousands of times
for every success!
This is different
than your research,
experiments don't have feelings!
The humans conducting them do,
and you know this one
can be solved, admit it!
[BOTH panting]
[door squeaks]
[DARU]
Okarin?
I'm sorry, I can't.
So, that's it, then.
He's a lost cause.
No, I believe
there's still hope.
You serious?
I lost to Kurisu
in our experiments--
in our theories, too,
and certainly in fame.
But I took a hard look
in the mirror
and I found the strength
to keep going.
Because if I gave up,
I knew it would all be over.
And then I'd never know
if I had it in me to win.
When I talk to Okabe,
I see the same look in his
eyes that I used to have.
[OKABE]
Mayuri?
[MAYURI] Oh, Okarin?
What are you doing here?
[OKABE]
Honestly?
Just happened to be passing by.
What about you?
[MAYURI]
Same.
Or something like that.
We used to come here
all the time, remember?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
[MAYURI] That was even before
Daru started coming around.
When I would get done
with school for the day,
I used to go
straight over to the lab
and wait for you there.
All by myself.
Even though I was alone,
for some reason,
I never felt lonely.
It felt happy, like home.
But now, when I'm at the lab,
it does feel lonely.
[OKABE]
But nothing's changed, has it?
It's still the three of us,
you, me, and Daru.
[MAYURI]
I wish I could say for sure.
But it feels like
something's missing.
Like someone isn't there
who should be.
And it's not as lively or fun.
That can't be true.
It just can't.
Can't it?
[MAYURI]
Okarin?
[OKABE]
Hmm?
[MAYURI] I wonder if I made
the wrong choice, in the end.
[OKABE gasping]
Maybe I should
have made you go back,
like she wanted you to.
Mayuri, what?
Oh, Okarin.
Maybe you were supposed to go
to Makise and save her life.
But instead,
you sacrificed everything
so that I didn't have to die.
And because you did,
you stopped coming to the lab,
and you always look like
you're in unbearable misery.
No, you're wrong!
But am I?
You heard us talking,
didn't you?
At the lab this
afternoon, right?
I'm not wrong.
Don't ever think that!
[sobbing]
[OKABE]
Please push all of this
as far from your mind
as you can, Mayuri.
Stop it, now, I'm begging you!
I can't!
[OKABE] Everything is fine,
so stop it! Right now.
All is well,
and nothing can hurt you!
I don't want anything
to destroy the time we have.
--So, please!
--Then, tell me why!
Tell me why.
Why do your eyes
look so sad all the time,
like you're in pain?
Ever since that one day,
it's like you're
suffering so much
you can barely breathe!
[MAYURI]
You know who Orihime is, right?
It's the star called Vega.
But guess what?
Overseas they have
another name for it.
There they call it
Arclight of the Sky.
[OKABE crying]
Mayuri.