ASUNA: I wish we could see
real stars in Aincrad.
KIRITO:
Yeah, but this isn't so bad.
ASUNA:
I've never seen a shooting star
in the real world before.
Where I live,
the sky's too bright at night.
(GRUNTS) A city‐girl.
That explains a lot.
Oh, come on!
Don't even tease me like that!
(GRUNTS, CHUCKLES)
There's this one spot in my town
that's pretty famous
for stargazing.
It's even got
a tiny observatory.
ASUNA: Oh, I know!
Let's make a date to go see
the stars there someday!
KIRITO: Sure. Someday.
ASUNA: We just have to make sure
we survive long enough
to clear this game.
Yeah. And as soon as we do,
I'll get you a real ring.
Mm‐hm.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
KAYABA: On November 6th, 2022.
the NerveGear, a FullDive
virtual reality device,
launched its first game,
Sword Art Online.
Its developer, Akihiko Kayaba,
told the 10,000 players
who logged in,
they could not log out.
And not only were they trapped,
if a player died in‐game,
they would also die
in the real world.
Amid growing despair,
some took up swords,
hoping to clear the game.
Some became isolated
and took their own lives.
While others ended up
turning their swords
on their fellow players.
This nightmare continued
for what seemed like
an eternity.
Then, on November 7th, 2024,
a heroic player dressed
head‐to‐toe in black,
cleared the game
and set everyone free. Finally.
Close to 4,000 people died
in the end.
But with the death
of the game's creator,
Akihiko Kayaba,
the nightmare was over.
The players
who lived through it
are known as SAO survivors.
And slowly but surely,
they're getting back
their lives
in the real world.
INTERVIEWER:
Um, sorry to bother you folks.
I couldn't help but notice
those things you're wearing.
Huh? What, this?
It's an Augma!
MACHINE VOICE:
Welcome to Augma.
NEWSCASTER:
Ever since it was made
available to the public,
it has quickly become
the gadget to have.
Today,
we'll look into the Augma,
the next‐gen wearable device.
If you compare the Augma
with its predecessor,
the AmuSphere,
you might think since it doesn't
have a FullDive function,
it's a step backward,
technology‐wise.
But that's so totally not true.
The user's fully conscious
while using the Augma
and that opens up
a whole world of possibilities.
Isn't comparing the two systems
a little like comparing apples
to oranges, though?
The AmuSphere immerses
the user in a virtual reality,
while the Augma immerses
the user in augmented reality.
You're absolutely right.
And if you wanna talk
about safety,
the Augma doesn't come
with any of the risks
a FullDive rig has for users.
In fact, more and more people
have been using it for exercise
‐and to track health goals.
‐(GASP)
Now we'll take a look at the
system's newest, hottest game,
Ordinal Scale.
COMMENTATOR: The most exciting
feature about Ordinal Scale,
in my opinion, anyway,
is the ranking system.
Each player starts
with a number
that reflects their ranking
in the game.
The more a person plays,
the higher
their rank's gonna be.
Once you get your rank
high enough,
you can unlock rewards
outside the game.
Stuff like
products and services
from partner companies!
NEWSCASTER:
Would you look at that!
There's a discount
from a big online retailer
and early access to tickets.
There's exclusive
shopping sites
and a coupon for a free
extra large beef bowl, too!
Kids always go nuts
for freebies.
If they're that good
in the lower ranks,
imagine what the top rank
will get.
(LAUGHTER)
NEWSCASTER: When service
for the game started,
drones were launched to ease
the strain on the network.
They were strange at first,
but folks seem
used to them now.
One of the main reasons
the game is gaining popularity
is thanks to its mascot, Yuna.
She's the world's
first AR pop star
and a testament
to how far AI tech has
come over the years.
In fact, her mannerisms
are so life‐like,
some think she's actually human
and not a program.
COMMENTATOR: She's mysterious!
That's probably the main reason
she's so popular.
I just started collecting
her figures myself‐‐
NEWSCASTER:
Uh, Yuna's first live concert
is scheduled for the end
of this month
and tickets for it,
all 30,000 of them,
sold out almost instantly.
I had to get mine from a scalper
and they damn‐near cost me
my condo‐‐
The popularity
of Augma and Ordinal Scale
isn't slowing down anytime soon!
All right, we cleared it!
Good job, Silica!
Nice assist, Liz!
We all got a hundred points
for beating it.
Look! It says we each get
a free slice of cake! Sweet!
You guys play games
way too much these days.
I‐I never thought I'd hear that
coming from you!
Heck, every time we play,
we get points to shop at stores.
Might as well play
our butts off.
I bet deep down, you wanted
to play, too, didn't you?
(GRUMBLES)
Well, I love this thing.
It's super convenient.
LISBETH:
It lets you watch TV anywhere,
it's easier to navigate
than a smart phone
and the weather report's
a lifesaver.
Best of all, we can talk
to Yui whenever we want.
Yup!
(GIGGLES) You sound like you're
totally sold on the Augma!
Mm, I wouldn't say that.
But, hey, they did hand them out
to everyone going
to the survivor's school, right?
The least we do
is take them out for a spin
and see what they can do.
WAITRESS:
I'm sorry for the wait.
Here are your bonus treats
for clearing the game.
(ASUNA GIGGLES)
LISBETH:
(GIGGLES) Dibs on that one!
(GASPING, GIGGLING)
The AI's so sharp, it knows
what kind of cake we like.
(SILICA GIGGLES)
It does a thing
they call "Deep Learning".
‐Pretty thoughtful.
‐(HUMMING)
It's even more thoughtful than
certain people we know.
I hear it can even tell you
how many calories
are in that cake.
(CHOMPS, GASPS)
(BUZZES)
(LISBETH PANTING)
Wait up, Liz!
Where are you going?
(BEEPS)
Asuna?
(GIGGLES)
SILICA:
I still can't believe it.
All of us
at the survivor's school
got free tickets to go
to Yuna's concert.
Going to a concert's kinda weird
for a field trip.
I know. Everything about
that school is weird.
Yeah, but now you get to see
your girl crush.
(STUTTERS) What?
I‐I don't have a crush on her!
Who was belting out her songs
at karaoke with Suguha?
You know every line
to every song and I'll prove it!
♪ ("UBIQUITOUS DB" PLAYING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
♪ (SINGING IN JAPANESE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GIGGLES)
(CHEERING)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
You were great, Silica!
(SHUDDERS)
Kirito? You're gonna come
to the concert with us, right?
(STUTTERS)
Huh? I wasn't planning on it.
I'm not much of a fan,
if you wanna know the truth.
What?
You should go, it'll be fun!
Well, I don't know, maybe.
‐(SIGHS)
‐(GIGGLES)
Anyway, I gotta admit,
you can do a lot of cool stuff
with this gadget.
Still, I think FullDives
are more my thing.
You're kidding.
No. I guess I just got used
to living in different worlds.
‐(GROWLS)
‐(GASPS)
(LAUGHTER)
You doofus. You sound like
you wanna go back.
Oh! Speaking of Aincrad,
Do you guys think that rumor
about Ordinal Scale is true?
You know,
the one about boss monsters
from old SAO showing up in it?
Oh, right.
The mysterious event battles.
Really? Is it like some kind
of promotion?
LISBETH: I don't know.
I haven't had the chance
to check one out yet.
The locations are secret
till the last minute,
so it's hard for folks who don't
have a car to get there in time.
It'd be awesome to find out,
though.
ASUNA:
So all we need is a ride? Hmm.
(KIRITO GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(IN UNISON) Kirito!
(GRUNTS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Looks like we made it
just in time.
They released the location
a half‐hour ago.
And there's already
so many people here!
That means there'll be even more
by the time it starts.
KLEIN:
About time you showed up?
Sweet!
You brought Asuna with you!
No, I brought him!
He didn't want to come,
but after I beat the others
at rock‐paper‐scissors,
he didn't have a choice!
Huh? Yeah, whatever.
Guys, Let's show her
how badass we are!
(IN UNISION) Yeah!
‐MAN: All right!
‐MAN 2: It's gonna be awesome!
Kirito,
it's almost time to start.
Oh, right.
‐ Ordinal Scale , activate!
(GASPS)
ASUNA: That's...
KIRITO: The boss from Floor 10
in Aincrad.
Kagachi the Samurai Lord!
He looks exactly like him,
doesn't he?
Too bad we can't use
our sword skills here.
I wonder if he's gonna use
the same attack patterns.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(GASPS) Yuna?
I hope everyone's ready!
It's time to battle!
So, start the music!
♪ ("LONGING" PLAYING)
‐Uh...
‐Oh, awesome! Yuna's singing!
TOSANEKO: It's a special stage
with a bonus!
(GASPING)
(GROWLS)
(ALL YELLING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(ROARS)
‐(MEN LAUGHTER)
‐I'm gonna piss myself!
‐How do we beat this thing?
‐He's frigging huge!
What do you say, Kiri‐dude?
(PANTING) No, wait! Time out!
Time out! (SCREAMS, GROANS)
(KAGACHI GROANS)
(GRUNTING)
Don't let your HP hit zero!
Your rank will get docked!
I know that!
(GASPING)
Aw, man. Our guns didn't
do jack to it at this range.
‐No way am I gonna get up close!
‐Hey!
Come on, you guys!
That bonus has our name on it!
(CHEERING)
I got it!
KLEIN: Nice block!
(PANTING)
Tank!
I'm on it!
(CLANKING)
(HISSING)
Eight showed up. Perfect.
(PANTING)
Body feels heavy.
This isn't like VR at all.
‐(GROWLS)
‐It's coming for you!
‐Kirito!
‐(KIRITO GRUNTS)
(GASPS, GROANS)
(GROANS)
‐KIRITO: Whoa!
‐(GROWLS)
Holy crap! It's hard to move!
You're just
a little out of shape, is all!
(PANTING) I'm not out of shape!
The hell's he doing?
‐Watch it, I got the kill‐shot!
‐Huh?
Oh, crap.
‐Nice one!
‐(MEN GASP)
Rank 2?
(GROWLS)
He's making his killer move!
Tanks! Follow me!
Nice hit, man! Come on!
Yes! Wait for me!
(CHEERING)
(CLANKING)
(GRUNTS)
‐Move! Retreat!
‐Right behind you!
All right!
Switch.
Go!
(CHEERING)
‐That was awesome!
‐Yeah!
Congratulations
on defeating the boss!
I just boosted
everyone's points!
(GASPING, CHEERING)
YUNA:
And I have a special reward
for the player who worked
the hardest!
(CHEERING)
‐Yeah!
‐Yes!
Oh.
(GASP)
You're this battle's MVP.
Congratulations!
(ALL GASPING)
See you at the next battle!
(CROWD GASPING,
INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Nice job, Asuna.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So that guy's number two?
He's a powerful player,
that's for sure.
KLEIN: Dude, my rank shot up
from just this one battle.
Look.
MAN:
Man, those SAO bosses pay out!
MAN 2:
If the other users find out,
this game's gonna get crowded!
KLEIN: Huh?
Well, well!
Looks like you barely moved up
in rank, Kiri‐dawg!
Like I care. I'm leaving
the AR raids to you guys.
(CHUCKLES) Make sure you get
the lady home safe.
Of course I will!
Hey, if the kid here gets
fresh with you, give me a call.
‐I'll come save you!
‐You got it!
‐(KIRITO GRUNTS)
‐(LAUGHTER)
ASUNA: See you!
KLEIN: Till next time!
Huh? What the heck's
an item doing here?
‐(GATE OPENING)
‐(GASPS)
What the‐‐? Oh, it's you.
Ah, so you wanna steal
my find, huh?
I don't give a damn
if you are ranked number two.
I ain't gonna give it up
that easy.
(TRAIN RUMBLING)
KLEIN: Man! That boss moved
the same as the one from SAO.
Wish I could say
I moved the same.
After all that running around,
my whole body's sore.
Can't believe you guys took it
down so quick.
For one thing,
Asuna and I fought it before.
Yeah, but still, it wasn't easy.
You could tell the other players
weren't used to working
as a team.
ASUNA: By the end of it,
Kirito was exhausted.
(GRUNTS) That's only 'cause
I'm not used to fighting in AR.
Hmm?
Oh, and you'll never guess
who showed up to cheer us on.
You know that girl, Yuna?
She gave us a reward‐‐
Huh? Yuna was at the boss fight
with you guys?
For real?
(PANTING)
(BOTH) What's she like?
That was pretty cool,
seeing her live.
But like a dumbass,
I forgot to put my name down
for one of those tickets.
Too bad you missed out, man.
When they were doing
those Ordinal Scale sign‐ups,
I scored myself a pair.
Yeah, I got a pair, too.
(BOTH) You got two?
Oh, come on! Hook me up!
(GRUNTS) All right, all right!
Get off! Stop begging,
I'll let you have one.
Stare.
(CHUCKLES) Yes, Leafa,
I'll give you a ticket.
‐Yay!
‐Thanks, man!
Uh, I just remembered,
I have kendo boot camp
next week. (SIGHS)
(LAUGHTER)
SILICA:
Is anyone else as weirded out
about this as I am?
I mean, what's up
with an old SAO boss showing up
at an Ordinal Scale battle.
If it were a tie‐in
between games,
wouldn't we have heard?
Mm‐hm. But I don't think
that's what's going on.
Argus, the company that used
to run SAO ,
was shut down a while ago.
What about the other players
at the event?
Did they know the boss
was from SAO , too?
Mm. No, I'm pretty sure
most of them didn't.
No one knew its attack patterns,
except us
and maybe one or two others.
Switch.
Isn't that the impression
you got?
Yeah. Most of them
never saw it before.
The thing is, if the old bosses
from SAO keep showing up,
it's only a matter of time
before folks start catching on.
And those battle events
are where the points are at.
Sounds like someone's trying
to bring old Aincrad
to the real world. Damn.
So what?
The Augma's nothing like
the NerveGear,
so no one's gonna die.
It's safe.
Anyway, Yui,
see if anything's fishy.
Okay, Daddy!
Heck, if I can hang out
with Yuna,
‐I'll totally go to a battle!
‐Me, too!
(WHISPERS) And next time, he'll
give me a ride on his bike.
I wish these events
would happen at better times
and at places
that are easier to get to.
That's what us guys
in Fuurinkazan are for!
If any of you ladies need
a ride,
just pick up the phone
and we'll pick you up!
Yeah,
that's what worries us, Klein.
‐But! Oh, you suck.
‐(LAUGHTER)
‐(SIGHS) Yuna.
‐(CAWS)
(YUNA HUMMING)
EIJI: What's wrong, Yuna?
What is this thingy?
Proof that everyone loved
your singing.
Really? This little guy?
YUNA: Hmm.
There'll be plenty more
where that came from...
after I get my revenge on them.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
I'm heading out now, Kazuto!
Okay. Have fun at boot camp.
You gonna change out
of those sweats anytime soon?
Yeah, well,
I'm just gonna stay home today.
And research some colleges.
That's good, but you should
get some exercise, too.
Grab a shinai and go swing it
around outside, at least.
Yeah, maybe. If I feel like it.
Don't forget to bring back
some of those‐‐
Whatever. You know, you should
try using the Augma more.
You could win
a free gym membership!
Well, see you!
(GRUNTS)
AR's everywhere I look
these days.
(SIGHS)
Link start!
Asuna! Hey.
Hey, you! So, what's going on?
Is Leafa coming?
No. She just left
for that Kendo boot camp.
‐Is she gone for long?
‐A few days.
Waking up in the morning's gonna
be tough. She's my alarm clock.
(GIGGLES) Dork!
Even though she's gone,
make sure you eat.
Of course! You know,
I can cook for myself.
If you say so.
But when you have stuff
on your mind,
you tend to forget things
like eating right.
Daddy only makes pasta with one
ingredient, pepperoncini.
TMI, Yui. TMI.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Kirito,
I was thinking about our plans.
My mom said she'd like
to meet you one of these days.
(STUTTERS) Yeah,
one of these days. Sure.
Mm.
(BEEPS)
They postponed
another event quest in ALO.
Again?
I just checked
and in the last two weeks,
ALO has had a 30 percent drop
in logins.
I guess it's because everyone's
busy playing Ordinal Scale.
Yeah, maybe. For now.
But I'm sure
they'll come back eventually.
Yeah.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(WATER SPLASHING)
Huh?
Hey, Asuna! Right on time!
KLEIN:
Thanks for coming out tonight.
Hope that text
didn't wake you up.
Oh, no. I wasn't in bed yet.
You caught me taking a bath.
(GASPING)
(STUTTERS)
You're missing
one of your friends.
Oh, yeah. We sent him a message,
but he hasn't called back yet.
How about you go on ahead,
we'll jump in once he gets here.
Okay.
But you better hurry.
Otherwise, I'm going to scoop up
all your points for myself.
(STUTTERS)
Hey, let's not be greedy!
‐(LAUGHTER)
‐(ASUNA GIGGLES)
‐See you in there.
‐Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
♪ (INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CAWING)
YUNA: Is everyone ready?
(MEN GASPING)
‐Yeah!
‐Wooo!
It's time to battle!
So, start the music!
♪ ("DELETE" PLAYING)
(CAWING)
KLEIN: Crap, Yuna showed up!
We gotta get in there!
Is Dale gonna show, or what?
MAN: Damn it. That loser
still hasn't answered my text.
We better hurry,
or we'll miss out on that prey!
EIJI: Actually,
tonight, you're the prey!
(GASPING)
What's a boss doing here?
♪ (SINGING IN JAPANESE)
‐MAN 2: It's a new song!
‐MAN 3: Aw, yeah!
(GRUNTING)
I'm impressed.
(GRUNTS)
EIJI: I can see why they were
some of the best
in the Assault Team.
(GRUNTS)
EIJI: But...
I'll teach them the difference
between AR and VR.
(CHEERS)
Oh, yeah! Bring that bonus!
(GASPING)
VR never hurt like that, did it?
(GRUNTS)
Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
(GRUNTING)
Come on, don't be like that.
Bastard.
(GROANS)
‐Now let's have some fun.
‐(GROANS, SCREAMS)
(CRACKS)
(SCREAMS)
(MEN GROANING)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
EIJI: Here. You dropped this.
(GROANS)
‐Now keep your eyes open.
‐(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(SNARLING)
(PANTS)
(GROWLING)
‐(CAWING)
‐(GUNFIRE)
It's winding up.
It's prepping
for its big attack!
‐You Tanks, draw its aggro!
‐(STUTTERS) Okay.
(CAWING)
Its killer move is coming.
When you see it hover,
aim for the wings!
Huh? Right!
Everyone moves in,
once it hits the ground!
You got it!
(CAWING)
‐Here, chickie, chickie!
‐(CLANGING)
(GROWLS)
Fire!
‐Go!
‐(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
MAN: Oh, shit!
(GASPING, CHEERING)
(MEN CHEERING)
(SIGHS)
Yo, you were amazing out there.
Nice strategy!
Yeah, you were awesome!
You play any other games?
(STUTTERS) Huh? Oh, uh...
YUNA: Hello again!
‐(GASPS)
‐Congratulations!
‐YUNA: Oh.
(GROANING)
Oh, well. See you later, Asuna.
EIJI: Lightning Flash Asuna.
Death isn't permanent
in Ordinal Scale.
And without the fear of death,
a player's potential
is unlimited.
Next time we meet in‐game,
I'll show you my potential.
(SIREN WAILING)
Here's the latest
on Ordinal Scale,
the AR game
everyone's talking about.
Players are telling us
that some of the bosses
from SAO 's old Aincrad,
have been showing up
in OS' event battles.
The word on the forums is,
a player can rack up a boat‐load
of points at those raids.
And not only that,
there's a good chance
you'll catch Yuna singing
at one of them!
(GIGGLES)
Leveling up and seeing Yuna
would be awesome!
Easy now!
As we all know, Sword Art Online
was shut down for good.
But I bet you didn't know
that there's been a ton
of new interest in it,
thanks to a book
that came out last month called
The Complete
SAO Incident Report.
Huh. Hmm.
Talk about jumping
on the bandwagon late.
I wonder
if the book's popularity,
along with the recent spike
in Augma users,
are the reasons
for the huge drop in logins
on the two big VR games,
ALO and GGO.
Do you think people
are getting bored with VR?
I have no idea, so let's ask
some familiar faces,
who might be able
to shed some light
on what's going on
in the VR world.
Take it away!
In the next ALO tourney,
I want to fight someone that'll
have me shaking in my boots.
Less players means
less challenge for me.
Hell, they might as well
give me the trophy now.
Yeah, well, you didn't win
last time, did you?
This world holds a special place
in our hearts
and there's no way
we're going to abandon it.
Yes, it's true. There are less
players in Sylph territory now.
We can't hold major events like
we used to, which is a shame.
But if you want to know
the truth, I'm not worried.
I'm sure
everyone will be back someday.
Why'd you desert me, Fukajiro?
I got a new grenade launcher
for you and everything!
You know how hard it is
to get one of these?
‐(GRUNTS) Where are you, Leafa?
‐Come back!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
EMCEE: Eh, sorry about that.
And now, please welcome
our surprise guest. Enjoy!
‐How's everyone doing tonight?
‐(CROWD CHEERING)
There's just four days left
till my first live concert!
I hope you're all
looking forward to it.
(CHEERING)
♪ ("UBIQUITOUS DB" PLAYING
OVER STEREO)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
‐Hi, Daddy! Good morning.
‐Good morning, Yui.
(YAWNS)
‐Where are we?
‐Oh.
This is the battlefield
Asuna played on last night.
She's putting a lot of effort
into this game, huh?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, she is.
(GASPS)
Is there something special
about that day?
Yup.
That's when I promised Asuna
I'd take her up to Mt. Doudaira
to watch the meteor shower.
(GASPS) That sounds fun!
Can I go, too? Can I?
What do you think? Of course!
Goodie! I'm gonna wear
something cute!
(GIGGLES)
Back in SAO,
we promised each other
that if we got out, we'd‐‐
Hey, Daddy!
This would be a great time
to do some fight training
for Ordinal Scale.
What?
Mommy said she was worried
about you
not getting enough exercise.
Go on,
show her how cool you are,
or your marriage
will be in trouble!
(GRUNTS)
Ordinal Scale, activate.
This doesn't feel right at all.
There's like a lag,
or something.
It's a different physical
sensation. That's all!
(SIGHS)
Practice is the only way
to get better!
(GRUNTS)
(PANTS) Maybe if I‐‐
(GASPS)
Oh, I'm sorry!
Who are you?
(GASPS)
(MUMBLES)
‐Did you see that, Yui?
‐Yes.
She didn't have an NPC tag.
She wasn't a player, either.
Then, is she some kind
of AR ghost?
No, Daddy. That's impossible.
I guess it is.
It looked like
she was saying something.
By the way her mouth moved,
I think she said the words,
"Look for...",
but that's all I could tell.
‐(GASPS)
‐I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry I went without you
last night.
No, that's okay. I don't mind.
YUI: Mm.
By the way,
at that last battle we were at,
you said you saw
some other SAO survivors.
Yeah.
That one player ranked second.
Really? That guy, huh?
I think he was in the Knights
of the Blood Oath. Maybe.
"Maybe".
Yeah, it's like, it's him,
but he's different
than he was in SAO.
ASUNA: Back then,
he went by "Nautilus"
and I remember
he had potential.
I also remember he couldn't go
on boss raids with us,
because he was afraid of dying.
KIRITO: Well, he's definitely
changed his playing style.
His agility in AR
is unbelievable.
Like a gymnast, or something.
Hmm. Did you talk to him?
Mm‐mm. I didn't know how
he'd react to seeing me again.
Still we were in the same guild,
so I'm a little concerned
about him.
It's hard to drop
being second‐in‐command, huh?
‐Watch it, soldier!
‐(BOTH LAUGH)
KIRITO: Hey, Asuna,
have you heard any stories
about this park?
You know, like, about ghosts.
Oh, my God, would you stop.
You know how freaked out I get,
talking about stuff like that.
I know, I know! I'm sorry.
(GRUNTS)
Anyway, Kirito,
let's talk about how
we're going to break the news.
Uh, "news"?
My mom knows
something's up with us,
so she's been grilling me
about you.
‐Oh, right, that news.
‐Mm‐hm.
She's not mad or anything.
But we should figure out
how to tell her.
Yeah. You're right.
Daddy! Mommy! I found
something out about the game!
YUI: I have something
to show everyone.
So far, when a boss monster
has appeared at an event,
it has always been at 9:00 p. m.
This is the location
where Mommy and Daddy
fought Kagachi the Samurai Lord
the other day.
And this is the location
where Mommy fought last night.
In a few seconds,
you'll see the locations
where the other
nine bosses appeared.
I'll also superimpose
a flattened map
of Old Aincrad over it.
No way!
Every place
a boss showed up in OS
lines up with a dungeon
from Old Aincrad!
The admin seem to have picked
open spaces in the city,
with coordinates that most
closely match the dungeons.
With this,
we can make certain predictions.
For example, tonight at 9:00,
a boss will most likely appear
at the Ebisu Garden Place
in Shibuya.
SILICA: Oh, this is great!
If we know where it's going
to be, we can go, too!
Won't your parents mind
you're out that late?
Mine won't, as long
as I'm hanging with you guys.
They're so weird.
If this was VR,
they'd pitch a fit.
‐Yeah, I bet!
‐(SQUAWKS)
(SIGHS)
Well, have fun, guys.
I have to work tonight,
so I can't make it.
How about you?
Are you gonna go to this one?
Nah. I'll pass on tonight.
Oh, jeez! Are you still not used
to fighting in AR?
Nope.
LISBETH:
Oh, well, suit yourself.
‐Darn it.
‐Huh?
All right, ladies!
Let's gear up
and show that Yuna chick
how us veteran players
like to party! (GIGGLES)
(IN UNISON) Yeah!
KIRITO:
By the way, where's Klein?
Who knows? He's probably
somewhere in Ordinal ,
grinding for points,
or something.
You know, I saw him last night,
right before the battle started.
But I don't think
he ever actually joined it.
They were waiting
on one of the other
Fuurinkazan guys to show.
Oh, yeah?
What sucks about AR battles
is you have go to
an actual place to participate.
Speaking of going places,
we should figure out
when we're all going to meet up
to go see the meteor shower.
‐(GASPS)
‐(GRUNTS) Shh!
You know what? We should
hammer out tonight's plan.
LISBETH: Okay, so where does
everyone wanna meet? Ideas?
‐Yui.
‐Yes, Daddy?
I wanted to keep
the meteor shower thing
a secret from the others.
Ooh! I'm so sorry.
Eh, it's okay. You didn't know.
Anyway, about the boss location
data you got,
could you send it
to my cell later on?
Yes! I'd be happy to!
(PHONE VIBRATING)
‐ Hi, Kirito, it's me.
‐Oh, hey, Asuna.
Hang on a second.
That is some plain pasta.
Yeah, I know.
It's the only recipe
my cooking app recommends,
so I'm going with it.
Your diet is so not balanced,
it's not even funny.
Here's an idea.
How about you make me some
of your ragout rabbit stew?
Right, I'll just whip one up.
I know!
What if I got some ingredients,
came over
and made something like it?
Oh, sure! That'd be great.
Hey, so about that ghost
you mentioned earlier today.
Huh?
You asked if I heard
about a ghost in Yoyogi Park?
(STUTTERS) Oh, right.
Anyway, I did some digging.
Some players say
they've seen a ghost.
Not in Yoyogi Park,
but in other places.
They say it looks
like a young girl in a hoodie.
(STUTTERS) You're kidding me.
What's wrong?
Wait, did you see her?
(STUTTERS) I didn't!
But like, maybe whoever saw it,
just saw an NPC instead! Maybe.
Mm. Maybe...
Oh, by the way, I found the tent
and sleeping bag.
They look like
they're good to go.
That's great!
It's a good thing
you have stuff like that.
Don't forget to thank your dad
for letting us borrow them!
Mm. Sure.
I can't wait. This'll be fun!
Bye, Klein.
Leader of the Fuurinkazan guild.
We sure had a big crowd
last night, huh?
Yeah, I guess we did.
The next one
will be even bigger.
Yeah? (GASPS)
Don't tell me
you're interested in this.
So many words. It looks boring.
No. It reads like a diary
of my memories.
Hm. The swordsman said,
"Once I draw my other sword,
the battle's over for you."
He sounds totally cool! Come on,
read the rest of it to me!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(BEEPS)
(GASPS, SCREAMS)
I finally found you.
I didn't know you were looking.
Well, you're not a ghost,
that's for sure.
Hey, who are you?
Is there something
you want me to find?
No, wait!
(PHONE BUZZING)
Hello?
AGIL: Hey, it's me.
About time you picked up.
Sorry. I was on the road.
What's up?
I found Klein.
He's in the hospital in Yoyogi.
Been there since last night.
His arm's all busted up.
What? He get in an accident?
I don't know. He said
he ran into some trouble
on the way to one of them
Ordinal Scale battles.
That's all I got
before he conked out.
Damn.
Let me know
when you find out more.
Yeah. You be careful
on that bike, man.
Daddy?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Gosh, I hope Yuna shows up
to this battle.
Silica, what do you think
the deal is with Yuna?
I mean,
do you think she's a program,
like what the developer says?
Or do you think
she might actually be human?
Well, I'm pretty sure
she's not a human.
But she also doesn't seem
like an AI, either.
Hey, if you ask me,
I can't think of a single human
that can sing with such
a crystal‐clear, flawless voice.
So you're saying my voice
isn't crystal‐clear, is that it?
(CHUCKLES)
You sound good, for a human.
Liz, I'm never going to karaoke
with you again.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, come on. I'm sorry.
It's starting.
(GROWLS)
(GRUNT, GASP)
Is everyone ready?
It's time to battle!
So start the music!
Yuna!
♪ ("LONGING" PLAYING)
We so lucked out!
You ladies ready
to get tons of points tonight?
(BOTH) Yeah!
I hate it
when I have to be the tank!
(LISBETH AND SILICA SCREAMING)
(ALL GASP)
Our plan worked!
"Worked"?
We almost got squashed!
(CHUCKLES)
Hot damn! You girls are kicking
all the ass out here.
(BOTH GIGGLE)
(SQUEAKS)
Come on, slow pokes!
Try and keep up!
Hey!
Those are our points, buster.
Ordinal Scale, activate!
‐Daddy?
‐(SHUSHES)
I think I know her
from somewhere else.
Your name's Nautilus.
We were in the Knights
of the Blood Oath together.
These days,
I go by a different name, Asuna.
Eiji?
‐(GRUNTS)
‐(CLANKS)
ASUNA:
You play this game really well.
(SCREAMS)
EIJI: I'm not who I used to be.
And you've gotten less intense.
Oh, really?
Yeah. Back then,
you were tougher.
I know her.
Going down!
(MEN GASP)
It's almost time.
(CHEERING)
Move in! Everyone, attack!
(ALL YELLING)
What the‐‐?
Is another boss showing up?
(SQUAWKS)
‐Pina!
‐Oh! Phew!
‐It's tiny!
‐(SIGHS)
(GIGGLES) Did you come
to help us fight?
(SQUAWKS, SNARLS)
(GASPS)
(SHUDDERS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SQUEALS, GROANS)
Silica! This way!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Daddy! That boss is called
Dorcel the Chaos Drake!
It lived way up on Floor 91!
KIRITO: Floor 91?
Let me at that thing!
KIRITO: Oh, shit!
(SQUEALING)
Why are you mad at me?
What did I do?
(GRUNTS) I'm sorry‐‐ Ah!
(GRUNTS) Silica!
(PANTS) Silica!
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
Asuna? Come on, Asuna, wake up!
(GROWLS)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Asuna!
(GASPS) Are you okay?
(GASPS)
You dick!
What the hell's your prob‐‐?
(GULPS)
(SCOFFS) You're pathetic.
You might've been
the greatest swordsman in VR,
but you're nothing in AR.
Son of a bitch!
(GRUNTS)
Hey, you!
Ever hear of game etiquette?
(ROARS)
Time's up!
(GASPING, INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
See you later!
Wait! What about the bonus?
Hey, I thought
you were gonna help Asuna!
MAN: Please kiss me!
(PANTS)
Asuna! Are you okay?
(MOANS)
‐(GASPS)
‐Well, this sucks.
Better luck next time.
(GASPS)
(MOANS)
I'm sorry, Asuna. This is all
because I was being stupid.
Can you believe
that number two guy
pushed Silica like that?
What an asshole!
KIRITO: Uh‐huh.
Nice save, Asuna.
That's another reason
they made you
second‐in‐command back in‐‐
Hey, what's wrong?
Did you get hurt?
Mm‐mm. No, it's nothing.
KIRITO:
Want me to take you home?
‐ASUNA: Mm‐hm.
‐SILICA: We'll help you up.
LISBETH: Hang onto my arm.
Good night, Asuna.
I'll call you tomorrow.
‐Kirito?
‐Yeah, what's up?
I, uh, I was wondering if you
still remembered the day we met.
Sure. It was on Floor 1
of Aincrad.
That boss raid meeting?
Yeah. Right. And then, you‐‐
Then you asked me to join
your party, didn't you?
Uh‐huh. I still can't believe
I had the guts
to even talk to you.
(GRUNTS)
(GIGGLES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
This is so cool. You can already
see the lake from here.
No, you can see the lake, I...
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Kirito, you shouldn't be
out here on your own!
Kirito?
(PANTING)
Kirito!
Who are you?
(GASPS) I'm...
(GASPS, PANTING)
A dream.
Kirito.
Why can't I remember?
‐(BUZZING)
‐(KIRITO GRUNTING)
Are you okay?
What's going on?
Can't you sleep?
Why are you sitting in the dark?
‐(BEEPS)
‐(GASPS)
Thanks for coming.
I'm sorry if I woke you.
It's okay. Did something happen?
(RUSTLING)
This cabin...
About how long
would you say we've lived here?
Well, we bought it in SAO,
so it's been
two and a half years now?
It has, hasn't it?
Asuna?
‐What...?
‐I knew it. I can't remember.
What do you mean? What?
Everything that happened
in Aincrad.
I can't recall any of it.
The first time you and I met.
All the battles we fought.
Us living here together.
(STUTTERS) What the heck
are you talking about?
You're joking, right?
In the last few hours,
the memories I had of SAO
faded away.
There's nothing left now.
I'll have to go
through all the data
before I can say
for certain what happened.
But by the looks of it,
Asuna's brain seems
to have undergone
some kind
of limited memory scan.
KIRITO: Limited memory scan?
So like, whatever did this only
targeted her memories of SAO ?
How's that even possible?
I can think of one way,
actually.
If she were put in a situation,
which forced her to recall
moments in SAO ,
the single neurons connected
to those memories
would be identified.
Then by showering the neurons
with electron pulses,
the image of each memory
is scanned.
In the past few days,
there've been multiple reports
of people with symptoms
similar to Asuna's.
It could be a coincidence,
but I doubt it.
Each patient had something
in common.
They all played
that AR game's event battles.
KIRITO:
Then the Augma's causing it.
DR. KURAHASHI:
I can't be certain of that yet.
Is Asuna going to be all right?
Well, as of right now,
I don't see any sign of actual
physical damage to her brain.
My theory is, her ability
to recall her memories
was affected
because the electron pulses
degenerated her spine.
Unfortunately, I can't tell
whether or not she'll show
any further symptoms
until I run some more tests.
Wait, so you're saying
there's still a chance she'll
lose even more of her memories?
(GASPS)
(CLOCK DINGING, TICKING)
ASUNA: I'm sorry, Kirito.
Don't worry.
You can still remember
what happened lately, right?
Mm‐hm.
This doesn't mean you're never
gonna remember SAO again.
You will, you'll see.
Asuna?
What's wrong, Asuna?
(GASPS) Asuna!
‐(CROWD MURMURING)
‐NURSE: Are you okay?
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
KIRITO: Well?
I'm sorry, Kirito.
I can't remember
anything about SAO.
I remember when we bought
this place in ALO,
but not when we first got it.
Everything about SAO 's a blank.
(SOBS)
‐Mommy!
‐I'm sorry.
I hate that I can't remember
the life we had back then.
I'm going to try to find out
what's really going on
in Ordinal Scale.
I'm sure I'll find
some kind of clue
that'll help you get
your memory back.
Mm. Thank you, Yui.
Even if I can't remember it now,
this really is the place
we called home back then,
isn't it?
Yeah.
I'll go make us some tea.
Oh, I wanna help!
No. I can make it.
The change of pace
will do me good.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SOBBING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
Now, I'm even more powerful
than Lightning Flash
and the Black Swordsman.
Who would've thought?
If it weren't for Ordinal Scale,
I'd still be nothing.
(HUMMING)
Soon, I'll make good
on the promise I made her.
(BEEPS)
Hello?
KIRITO: So how's your arm doing?
Eh, it's not too‐‐ (GRUNTS)
I feel worse about making
you guys worry.
Do you feel any,
I don't know, different?
Huh?
Do you remember
what happened in SAO ?
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS) No.
If I try and think about it,
it's like my head's all stuck
in this big‐ass fog.
Well, it's not like it was
all fun and games for us, right?
I don't know.
Maybe it's better
I don't remember.
I can't wait. This'll be fun!
MACHINE VOICE: Welcome to Augma!
KIRITO: Damn! (SIGHS)
(GASPS) Launch search
for Ordinal Scale rankings.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(PANTS)
‐Hey!
‐Hmm?
Oh, uh! Sorry.
‐Let's go, man.
‐Yeah.
I can't tell
if it's a side effect
due to a glitch in the system,
or a deliberately designed
feature.
If it's the latter and someone
did this intentionally,
I'm afraid
this is only the beginning.
Let me get this straight.
You're saying that if any
of the other SAO survivors
play Ordinal Scale,
there's a chance they'll lose
their memories, too.
Just like Asuna?
KIRITO: If I'm not careful,
it could happen to me, too.
If I can't remember those
two years with her,
will I also forget I love her?
I'm sorry, Daddy!
I couldn't find
the player called Eiji.
I used his name and visual data
from the last battle,
but the search
didn't turn up a thing.
Oh, well...
Don't give up, Daddy.
While you're fighting the boss,
I'll be gathering data.
I'm sure I'll find something
to go on!
I know you will.
‐I'm counting on you.
‐Right.
SINON:
Well, well! Look who it is.
YUI: Huh?
KIRITO: What are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
You just told everyone
not to fight the bosses
and here you are.
I know.
But it really is dangerous.
If a boss kills you, you'll lose
your memory like Asuna.
(CHUCKLES) I'll be fine.
I'm not an SAO survivor
like you guys.
If I don't have
those memories to scan,
nothing's gonna happen to me.
Right, Yui?
Yes. You should be safe.
I think.
Yeah, but we don't know if‐‐
If you're really that worried,
then you'll just have
to keep me safe, won't you?
If anyone can keep her safe,
it's you, Daddy.
(BOTH) Ordinal Scale, activate!
‐(MEN GASPING)
‐KIRITO: What the‐‐?
That's Dire Tusk,
the boss from Floor 18!
What happened
to Floor 13's boss?
I just checked
and a total of ten monsters
have appeared at different
locations across the city!
They're pulling out
all the stops tonight.
YUI: Dire Tusk is here,
because the admin shuffled
the locations around!
(MEN MURMURING)
Crap, that's Dire Tusk,
all right.
Come on!
(GROANS)
(GROWLS, SQUEALS)
It's gonna wind up
for an attack next.
Then let's light him up!
(GUNFIRE)
Awesome!
He's like a sitting duck!
‐No, get away!
‐(GROWLS)
‐(CHAINS RATTLING)
‐(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS) Oh, crap!
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
‐(BEEPING)
‐(GASPS)
(CHEERING)
(YELLS)
Pace yourself!
(GRUNTS)
‐(ROARS)
‐(GRUNTS)
(ALL GROANING)
(PANTING)
(SQUEALS)
(SCREAMING)
(PANTS, GRUNTS)
He didn't show up tonight.
Nice one.
Yeah. Thanks to you.
Take me out for cake
and we'll call it even.
How about a coupon
for a free beef bowl instead?
Do I look like
I want a beef bowl?
I'll settle for a ride home
on your bike, cheapskate.
Yuuna?
(GASPS) Hey, wait!
Who are you?
I'm sorry, Daddy.
I was following a clue,
but I got blocked by a firewall.
During the battle just now,
I found out that a mysterious
program activated
right when a SAO survivor
took on critical damage
from the boss.
Son of a‐‐ (GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
‐You want a drink?
‐Mm‐mm.
‐(SIGHS)
‐(BEEPS)
(SIGHS)
‐Look for‐‐
‐Of course!
Yui! That girl in the hoodie.
You know
which direction she pointed
‐each time we saw her?
‐Yes, I have the coordinates.
Bring up a map of Tokyo
and show me where they all lead.
They crisscross in Ookayama!
You know
what that building is, Yui?
That's where the Touto
University of Engineering is.
Why does she want me
to look there?
I'll cross‐reference
the school's database
and the player called Eiji.
It'll just take a second.
I know this guy.
YUI: That's
Professor Tetsuhiro Shigemura.
He designed the Augma.
KIRITO: He did, huh?
SHIGEMURA:
Based on the evidence,
the most glaring flaw
in a FullDive VR device
is the FullDive function itself.
When a person has to sever
their physical senses
to play a VR game,
that person is taking on
incalculable risks
to their health.
True, FullDive tech
has been applied
to activities other than gaming
such as communication, browsing,
and digital production.
But none of those activities
require all of one's senses.
Sight, sound and limited tactile
information are enough.
So instead of using
a dangerous FullDive device,
one should use an AR device,
which has been proven
to be safe and stable.
Are there any questions
on what we've covered so far?
Yes. You there.
Professor,
would you say AR devices
have certain risks
that VR devices don't?
If so,
what are your thoughts on that?
Yes, well, are you talking
about traffic accidents,
while wearing an AR device?
No. I'm talking about risks
like permanently altering
and damaging the user's
perception of reality.
FullDive tech
just makes a virtual world
seem like reality.
But AR tech
alters reality itself.
Don't you think
that's dangerous?
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
I'll answer that question
next time.
‐Class dismissed.
‐(ALL GASP)
KIRITO:
I'll cut right to the chase.
Do you know someone named Eiji?
He's the second rank player
in Ordinal Scale.
No.
But he was in your class
and he even took your lab.
I've had many students
over the years.
Okay, let's try
a different question.
Did you know that the Augma
is causing SAO survivors
to lose their memories?
Did you know
the Augma has a feature
users don't know about?
A feature that scans their brain
while they're wearing it?
(SIGHS) I didn't know
I was going to be interrogated.
Kikuoka told me you just wanted
to audit my class.
If the Augma does have
a dangerous feature built in,
it won't be long
before it's found out.
And once that happens,
the Augma's gonna be banned,
just like the NerveGear was.
And you?
You'll end up the same as your
former student, Akihiko Kayaba.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
But let's say the Augma
has this brain‐scanning function
you described,
why is it bad if someone
forgets about SAO ?
In the words of Nietzsche,
"Blessed are the forgetful,
for they get the better
even of their blunders."
So now ask yourself,
do you think those survivors
want to remember
their horrifying past?
(GASPS)
If you wish to speak further,
make an appointment.
I'm very busy, though,
so there's no guarantee
I'll be able to see you.
I didn't know you built
robots too, professor.
Thanks for your time.
(KIKUOKA ON PHONE) That's right.
Dr. Shigemura has a daughter.
Or rather, had.
She died two years ago.
KIRITO: Yuuna?
I'm sure you put
two‐and‐two together already,
but I might as well
confirm it for you.
The cause of death
was the NerveGear.
She was a victim of SAO.
Huh? Why would he do this?
What the hell's he trying
to prove?
Well, maybe he honestly
thinks he's doing good
by making
the SAO survivors forget.
Yeah, well,
I can't prove it yet,
but I'm sure the Augma's
dangerous to users.
I need your help.
Please, Mr. Kikuoka.
Shut down the service.
The Ministry of Economy
is tied up with this,
so we have to be careful
with how we proceed.
I am looking into everything
you've told me.
But I can't move without proof.
A bunch of the Ordinal Scale
players are SAO survivors.
And if they fight any
of the bosses from Old Aincrad,
you're gonna have a lot more
people losing their memories.
I know
and I'm doing the best I can.
I checked with the hospital
about Klein and his friends
and confirmed their symptoms
with the doctors.
But I'm more concerned
about their broken bones
than their memories.
You should take
your own advice and don't fight
any more bosses.
Your memories
are important to me, too.
Don't forget that.
Hey, what's up?
ASUNA: Nothing. I just wanted
to hear your voice.
Oh.
Listen, Asuna.
‐Is it cool if I come over?
‐Now?
Um, yeah.
Or later, if that's better.
No, now's fine.
I'd come to you, but I'm kind
of scared to go outside.
No, I get it.
I'll be at your place
in about 20 minutes.
I'm in Ookayama right now,
but traffic's not too bad.
Sorry.
The door was already open.
Heh, why do you sound
so nervous? It's okay!
My parents are both at work.
(STUTTERS) Yeah,
but it's my first time here.
Oh, crap. I should've brought
your folks a gift.
Like a plant, or something.
Don't be silly!
It's fine, I swear.
Come on, this way.
I was talking to someone today
and they said survivors like us
are better off forgetting
what happened in SAO.
I got to thinking and maybe
he's got a point there.
We saw a lot
of horrible things happen.
It was scary and sad.
But the memories
we have of those two years,
good and bad, are what shaped us
into the people we are today.
Everyone's been telling me about
how high‐tech your room is.
It's not what I thought.
In a way, it sort of reminds me
about your place in Selmburg.
I'll go bring us up
some drinks and snacks.
‐Yeah, sure.
‐Make yourself at home, okay?
(EXCLAIMS)
Uh...
ASUNA: To the future me.
It's been a long time since
I've written in this diary.
These days, I'm worried
I'll forget what's happened
to me since I came back
to the real world,
so I'll write how I feel now
in case I do.
I met Kirito four years ago,
but I only remember
the last two.
The moments with him,
I can still remember,
are precious, like jewels.
There's a good chance
Ordinal Scale
will cause me to forget things
more and more.
And that scares me.
But as long as I can
keep making new memories
with Kirito,
I should be fine.
My calendar says I'm supposed
to go to the mountains
in Saitama in a couple of days
to watch the stars with him.
But I don't remember the day
we made plans
to go there anymore.
I went back and read this diary
and from what I can tell,
Kirito said he wanted to give
me some kind of present.
I hope he'll forgive me
for not remembering what.
I want to get him something,
but since I'm not allowed
to have a job yet,
I'm going to use all my points
and whatever I have saved
to buy him a gift.
My beloved Kirito.
What will I do if I forget him?
What will I do if I forget
these feelings I have?
And what if it turns out
I can't make new memories
with him?
It scares me
to even think about it.
I pray that the person
I am tomorrow
doesn't forget the feelings
I have for him now.
‐(DOOR OPENS)
‐(GASPS)
It's okay. You can read
the whole thing if you want.
‐(GASPS)
‐(THUDS)
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I love you, Kirito. So much.
Even if I forgot everything
that happened in SAO ,
my feelings for you
will never ever change.
They won't for me, either.
I love you.
Always have. Always will.
I know.
I'm gonna get your memories
back, no matter what. I promise.
You know
I won't let you down, right?
Mm‐hm.
YUNA: Oh, a shooting star.
Well, Eiji,
tomorrow's the big day.
I get to be on stage
in an enormous arena
and sing for everyone.
Yeah. You nervous about it?
No. Not at all.
I finally get my chance
to sing for a huge audience.
How cool is that?
This performance
is gonna make me
the world's number one diva.
That's right.
Tomorrow's going to make you
the biggest and brightest
star of them all.
Hey! Would you please read
some more of that book to me?
Sure. You got it.
This time,
could you find the part in it
where you show up?
I wanna hear about you.
‐I'm not in it.
‐Huh?
I don't show up
anywhere in this thing.
I guess folks like us,
the ones who couldn't fight,
aren't worth remembering.
‐(PHONE RINGING)
‐Yes?
(GRUNTS)
SHIGEMURA: You're taking far
too long getting this done.
Someone's caught on
to our plan. You need to hurry.
Yes. I know that, sir.
I made sure all the pieces
are in place
for the final stage.
You're not having
second thoughts
about our deal, are you?
Not as long as you hold up
your end of it.
I will, sir.
By the way, about Yuna...
Lately, it seems like
she has other things
on her mind besides singing.
That's probably
her self‐preservation program.
If anything, it's proof
the plan is going smoothly.
If you say so.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Yuuna, right?
So where is this place?
Is it a dream?
The virtual world?
Dreams and virtual worlds
are the same thing,
more or less.
The second you wake up,
the experience
becomes a fleeting memory.
I guess.
Here's a thought,
maybe it's all just a dream.
Everything like
clearing that death game
and coming back
to the real world.
And what if,
when you open your eyes,
you wake up trapped
in Aincrad again?
Did you ever think about that?
I have, but I never wished
it was true, not even once.
And by the sound of it,
you're an SAO survivor, too.
Are you
Professor Shigemura's daughter?
Are you still alive?
Why'd you send me to your dad?
What do you want me to do?
Why would your dad wanna steal
Asuna's memories of SAO ?
What's the Augma really for?
♪ (SINGING "THE FIRST TOWN")
That song!
All I want is to go on singing.
It's all I ever wanted.
And I wanna save Asuna.
So are you gonna
tell me how or not?
Getting her memories back
isn't going to be easy.
The rank you have now isn't
nearly high enough to do it.
Well?
Don't just stand there. Wake up.
‐(SNAPS)
‐(GASPS)
Whoa, easy! You okay, guy?
‐Yeah.
‐(SIGHS)
What, you fell asleep playing
that Augma game?
Seems like everybody's got
one of those things these days.
Careful you don't fall
on your face.
(GULPS)
♪ (SILICA AND ASUNA SINGING
UBIQUITOUS DB")
You wanna know the truth,
I think Silica blames herself
for what happened.
LEAFA: I didn't even know.
If only I could've gone
to one of those battles.
Klein got himself hurt at one
and ended up in the hospital.
It's probably better
you stayed away.
You said it.
Kirito told everyone
not fight the bosses in OS
because it's so dangerous.
And then, he goes
to fight them by himself.
I sort of helped him
on the last one, though.
(GRUNTS)
But then, you know what?
I'm gonna make a video
to teach him some kendo moves.
Then he'll cruise through
those battles, no sweat.
Mm‐hm. Violence brings
siblings together.
Come on!
We're singing
the next song together.
We're here to practice,
remember?
The concert's tomorrow!
‐Take the mic and get in here.
‐(GASPS)
I don't know
if this is cheering her up.
("BREAK BEAT BARK" PLAYING)
What do you mean?
It looks like
Asuna's having fun.
If you say so...
‐(SIGHS)
‐Dude, you okay?
What's wrong?
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
YUI:
Multiple bosses have appeared,
just like last night.
But this time, it's the ones
from Floors 20 to 30.
I'm gonna take all of them
down tonight.
(GRUNTING)
I can't believe he's knocking
down its HP all by himself.
He's a badass.
(GRUNTS)
(STUTTERS) Jeez! Chill out!
What are you getting
so worked up for?
It's only a game.
‐Move!
‐(MEN GASP)
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTING)
It's time for a bonus stage.
Good luck, everyone.
‐(CHEERING)
‐We totally scored!
‐(ROARS)
‐(ALL GROANING)
(PANTS)
‐(SNARLS)
‐(ALL CHEERING)
(PANTING)
EIJI: Congratulations.
It looks like
you finally learned
how to handle yourself
in this game, Black Swordsman.
You bastard! (GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(SCOFFS)
(GRUNTS)
Instead of Yuna rewarding you,
I will.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Wow. Yuna's more popular
than I thought.
Ugh. My throat's sore
from karaoke.
That's what you get
for overdoing it.
Silica, thank you for yesterday.
(STUTTERS) Oh, sure!
Oh, man. Wish Klein
and Suguha could be here.
Wait. Where's Kirito?
He said he was going to stop by
the restroom first.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Okay, I'm here like you wanted.
You're gonna give me
her memory back,
or do I have to take it?
What's the rush,
Black Swordsman?
You called yourself
Nautilus back then.
Cool name for a guy
who wouldn't fight,
'coz he was too scared of dying.
I'm called Eiji now!
(SIGHS, SCOFFS)
Guess I can't escape my past.
I'm surprised you remember
a little runt like me.
Actually, I don't remember you.
A friend did.
Hmm?
A friend, like Asuna, I bet.
It's not enough you have her,
you probably want Yuuna, too.
‐What are you talking about?
‐Never mind.
You think you're so cool.
You know, there's a reason
I'm ranked second in this game.
Do you really think
you can beat me?
I won't know until I try.
Besides, it's not like
you're number one.
(SCOFFS)
(BOTH) Ordinal Scale, activate!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
♪ ("BREAK BEAT BARK" PLAYING)
(ALL GASPING, CHEERING)
♪ (SINGING IN JAPANESE)
SHIGEMURA:
I wish I could change things.
I used my position as chairman
of Argus' board of directors,
to get Yuuna a NerveGear
and a copy of SAO.
I was just trying
to make my daughter happy.
But in the end,
it was my stupidity
that killed her.
Yuuna!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Hah! I can see how everyone
believed you'd clear SAO.
You've got some moves!
Wish I could say the same
about you. Second rank my ass!
(SCOFFS)
(GASPS)
People only remember the players
who fought on the front lines.
But Yuuna and me?
We didn't fight,
so we get treated
like we didn't even exist!
Wait,
you guys were together in SAO ?
That's right!
And I was with her at the end.
I watched her vanish!
I hated myself
for being so weak!
The girl I loved was in danger
and I couldn't lift a finger
to save her!
Her brain had become so damaged
by the effects of the NerveGear,
it was impossible to save her.
But if I could acquire
the memories of her
from the other SAO players
and find a way to combine them,
the Deep Learning function
would do the rest.
And it could give my daughter
new life, as an AI.
(GRUNTS)
The numbers in
the Ordinal System are absolute.
Whoever is ranked number one
becomes immortal.
After all, that's how
you designed it, Kayaba.
Yuna, is it? It sounds like
"una", the Latin word for "one".
Aincrad was controlled
by a system
using cardinal numbers.
Ordinal Scale is controlled
by a system
using ordinal numbers.
A system I originally developed
for SAO,
but discarded early on.
It seems you resurrected it,
doctor,
and developed a new game.
The man I used to be
would've done the same,
had I been in your place.
But now, doctor,
the man I've become
believes in something greater.
An existence that can transcend
the system itself.
Who cares if we take away
everyone's memories of SAO ?
We're doing them a favor!
Let's see how good you are
without this!
(PANTING)
Goddamn you!
We all suffered back then.
But I won't lose to a guy
that rejects the past,
because he thinks
he suffered more.
Are you gonna give me
Asuna's memory back,
or do you wanna keep going?
‐(LAUGHS)
‐(GASPS)
(ALL CHEERING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(INHALES, EXHALES)
That was so fun!
(ALL GASPING)
EIJI: It's too late now.
Practically every SAO survivor
is upstairs.
In a few minutes,
we're going to start scanning
the brains of every survivor
and take their memories of SAO.
Their memories of that hell.
And then we'll bring Yuuna
back to life.
Huh? What're you talking about?
Like I said. It's too late now.
And you can't stop it.
‐(GRUNTS)
‐(LAUGHING)
KIKUOKA: Okay, so here's
what I learned from Kamura,
the company
that manufactures the Augma.
The drones flying inside
the stadium
are equipped
with a special function.
According to my source,
they can boost the output
of the Augmas wirelessly.
So, what does that mean?
It means if they run that
brain scan inside the stadium,
we might be dealing
with something worse
than just partial memory loss.
(GASPS) Holy shit!
You said it.
The scan could permanently
damage the brain
and might even kill people,
just like the NerveGear.
(PANTS)
(CLAMORING)
(GASPS)
KIKUOKA: I'll get the professor.
You get everyone
to take off their Augmas.
Hopefully,
they'll listen to you.
AGIL: Oh, my God!
Is this part of the show?
‐Let us out!
‐Open the door!
(BOTH GASP)
‐Asuna!
‐(AGIL GASPS)
Asuna! You okay?
(GROANS)
(GASPS) Kirito!
KIKUOKA: Damn it.
Looks like Kirito will have
to handle things
on his own in there.
Come on!
Yuuna?
Please, Dad.
You have to stop this now.
No. You're not quite ready yet.
(STUTTERS) But I don't want
to come back to life.
Of course you don't.
You're still an AI
and that's what
your self‐preservation program
is making you say.
It won't be long now,
so just be a good girl and wait.
But, Dad...
The AI crawler is collecting
all the data from the players.
She's almost done.
It's her final task.
She did a fine job.
You have to stop this!
If you run a high‐output scan
inside there,
those people might not just lose
their memories, they could die!
That is enough, Yuuna!
SHIGEMURA: I would happily
sell my soul to the devil,
if it meant
I could bring you back to life.
I swear I'd... do anything,
even if it meant I ended up
like Kayaba.
All I want
is to get you back in my life.
(GROANS) Step back!
KIKUOKA:
He's not making it easy for us.
That camera's recording.
Find out where it's connected.
SHIGEMURA: That should keep you
busy for a while, Kikuoka.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
EIJI: I'm sorry, sir.
I lost to one of the players.
But you can go ahead with
the brain scan on the crowd.
I can't wait to see Yuuna again.
The way she was.
SHIGEMURA:
You still have one last task
to finish, though.
What?
You have to give me
your memories of Yuuna as well.
Huh?
Of all the players in SAO,
you were the one who spent
the most time with her.
What did you expect?
Besides, if you can't
even master the equipment
I gave you,
what use are you?
What? But what about our deal?
You said you'd make it,
so I could be
with Yuuna forever!
Farewell.
(GROWLS)
(CROWD CLAMORING)
(GRUNTS)
(LISBETH GASPS)
(YUUNA WHIMPERS)
‐Yuuna!
‐Help me, Kirito!
If we don't stop this,
everyone here is going to die!
YUUNA: Once the average
of their emotive counters
passes 10,000,
a high output scan will activate
and destroy their brains!
I'm on it!
Everyone!
Take off your Augmas! Now!
Take them off, or you'll die!
(SIGHS) It's no use.
My dad put the bosses
in the other events,
so everyone here would fight,
thinking it's part of the game!
What am I supposed to do?
Go to the place
we met yesterday.
That was Floor 100
in Old Aincrad!
Go there and beat the boss!
It's our last hope. Sit down.
I'm going to unlock the Augma's
FullDive function now.
You can FullDive with the Augma?
The Augma's just a version
of the NerveGear
with limited functions.
Now get going!
(CLANGS)
(GRUNTS) I'm ready! (GASPS)
You guys...
‐Let's do this.
‐Yeah!
Good luck, Daddy!
‐Yui. Guard your mom.
‐Right!
ASUNA: Kirito!
Don't worry,
this won't take long.
We're the only chance
these people have
but I'm gonna need you
to wait here.
(GASPS)
Kirito...
Keep that safe,
till I get back, okay?
(GASPS)
(ALL) Link start!
No way!
So this is Floor 100,
The Ruby Palace!
Can't believe after two years,
we finally get
to take a crack at it!
Agil!
So you're the last boss
of SAO , huh?
Let's go!
(ALL GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
‐(YELPS)
‐(SCREAMS)
Switch out!
(GRUNTS)
‐Switch!
‐(BOTH SCREAMING)
(GROWLING)
Shit.
No way.
Oh, man.
How do we beat that thing?
(CLAMORING)
(GROWLS)
(GROANS)
YUUNA: I'm sorry, Asuna.
I'm the reason
your memory was stolen.
My father's collecting the other
SAO players' memories of me
from when I was alive
in Aincrad.
(GASPS)
YUUNA: He's using the old bosses
to force the survivors here
to remember
their fear of dying in SAO.
Then he'll run a scan
on their brains
to extract the memories.
If that happens,
it might end up damaging
everyone's brains permanently.
It might even kill them!
Oh, my God!
No, don't!
ASUNA: If I take it off
his head, he'll be saved.
But then,
what about the other players?
They're still in danger.
(THUDS)
(GASPS)
ASUNA: Yuuna, you died in SAO,
because you were brave enough
to leave the safe zone.
You fought a boss and tried
to clear a floor, didn't you?
I can't sit here and do nothing.
Yui? I'm going to help Kirito
and the others.
Okay, Mommy.
I'll join you in a little bit.
(INHALES) Link start!
Oh, no! (YELPS)
‐(YELPS)
‐Silica!
(GASPS)
‐Kirito!
‐Silica!
(WHIMPERING)
No!
Crap!
(ALL GASP)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS)
‐SILICA: Asuna!
‐I got you!
It's my fault! (SOBS) You lost
your memories because of me!
No, stop blaming yourself.
It's okay now.
(GASPS) Asuna!
(BOTH GRUNT)
Hi, guys. Sorry I'm late.
‐(CHUCKLES)
‐You okay to be here?
Mm‐hm. I'm ready to fight.
I'm not afraid anymore.
Good.
‐(GUNSHOT)
‐(BOTH GASP)
(ROARS)
(ALL GASPING)
Kazuto! Sorry I'm late!
(GASPS) Daddy, Mommy!
I brought everyone else, too!
‐This is gonna be fun!
‐Stay sharp, general!
Ha! We rule in VR!
(GRUNTS)
‐Skeena Guail!
‐Guy‐sah Oru‐muru!
(GUNFIRE)
She's a big lady!
‐They're here, too?
‐Yay!
Time's running out!
Hit it again!
Don't just stand there!
You've got work to do!
(GASPS)
‐What the‐‐?
‐(SQUAWKS)
Pina!
I loaded up your saved data
from the SAO server.
I thought you'd be
more comfortable this way.
I also brought your gear, Sinon!
(CLANKS)
‐All right! Let's do this!
‐ALL: Yeah!
(YELLS)
(CLANKS)
Hurry! Block it!
(SCREAMS)
‐You and me, Asuna!
‐Right!
Damn it!
Switch!
ASUNA:
I know what skill to use.
(SWORD CLANKING)
(YELLS)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(ALL CHEERING)
KAYABA: Now you really
have cleared the game, Kirito.
Kayaba?
You only have one thing
left to do.
(YUUNA GASPS)
(ROCKS RUMBLING)
(GRUNTS)
(SNARLING)
‐(GASPS)
‐(CLANKS)
(GASPS)
♪ (SINGING "SMILE FOR YOU")
♪ (SINGING IN JAPANESE)
It's Yuna!
(ALL CHEERING)
(STAMMERS)
Why is this happening?
I was so close, Yuuna! So close!
(SNAPS)
(GASPS)
Don't worry, Dad.
No matter what, I'll always
be in your memories.
Forever and ever.
(ALL CHEERING)
‐(GASPING)
‐(YUI GIGGLES)
You sounded great up there,
Yuuna.
Thanks a lot.
(GASPING)
The data for my primary body
was based on the resource script
of the boss from Floor 100.
Its language engine is what
allowed me to move around.
But the boss was defeated
and its saved data
will be initialized.
So now I have
to say goodbye to you.
No way.
It's not a bad thing.
I got to sing in front
of a huge audience,
so my wish was fulfilled.
I couldn't be happier.
Before I go,
I have to give this back to you.
Your fear of death
is what caused you
to lose your memories.
But you overcame it
and fought anyway.
I'm sure everything
will come back to you now.
YUUNA: You remembered
my wish, Eiji. Thank you.
(SOBBING)
NEWSCASTER: The AR idol, Yuna,
is making headlines again.
During her concert
at the New National Stadium,
several boss monsters
from Ordinal Scale appeared.
The promoters of the show
said today
that it was a surprise event
for the fans.
In other game‐related news,
Kamura Incorporated,
the company behind the Augma,
revealed
that their head of development,
Dr. Shigemura
of Toto Institute,
has decided to step down.
SILICA: Bet you're glad
to be out of that hospital.
LEAFA:
Yeah, how's your arm doing?
Ow! Nah, I'm kidding, it's fine.
But I'll be sticking
to VR games from now on.
LISBETH: But you got to meet
more girls in AR.
Eh, it's no big deal.
Nobody meets their dream girl
in games, anyway.
You better pray my wife
never hears you say that.
Yo, she gave up her ticket
for your broke ass.
‐Ow! What's your problem?
‐Apologize!
Um, guys, I brought
something back for everyone.
Where was this boot camp
you went to?
LEAFA: Shimane.
The place we stayed
didn't have computers.
If I didn't smuggle
in my Amusphere,
I would've died from boredom!
(BOTH) Eh...
By the way,
where's Kirito and Asuna?
They said
they had other plans tonight.
Anyone know what they're doing?
Oh, who cares about them.
If they're not here,
they're missing out.
Some friend.
I get discharged and he can't
come by for a drink?
He can suck it.
On second thought,
you can buy
your own drinks tonight.
You all owe me for that ticket.
You greedy‐‐
You got that ticket for free,
you cardboard‐sword dealer!
‐(LAUGHTER)
‐KLEIN: Oh, whatever.
At least I got ALO.
Now that it's hopping again,
maybe I'll meet
some new hotties.
AGIL: Nope.
ASUNA: You were right,
it gets dark up here.
Yeah. Can you see, Yui?
Yup! I can see
just fine, Daddy!
The color balance is skewing
a little green, though.
(CHUCKLES) For a while there,
I didn't think
we'd get to come here.
Oh, and in the end,
I left without telling my mom.
‐You what?
‐(GIGGLES)
You're kidding, right?
(CHUCKLES)
KIRITO: I'll talk to her
when we get back.
Do you remember what we promised
each other back in Aincrad now?
What, to go stargazing?
Well, yeah. That was part of it.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm kidding. I remember.
You said if we ever got out,
you'd give me a real ring.
‐Here. For you!
‐Um.
It's not fair if you're the only
one handing out presents,
so I got you one.
Thank you.
This time, put it on my finger.
And this time, for real.
‐YUI: Look! A shooting star!
‐ (BOTH GASP)
‐ASUNA: Wow!
‐YUI: Amazing!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
♪ ("CATCH THE MOMENT" PLAYING)
SHIGEMURA:
Why all the mystery, Kikuoka?
What did you bring me
down here for?
I appreciate you getting
the charges against me dropped,
but it's time you told me
what this is about.
KIKUOKA: Actually, doctor,
I want to talk about the future.
I've been keeping a close eye
on your research.
And now, I feel like I've seen
how far a top‐down AI can go.
But I have my sights
on a different kind of future.
You're the head
of the Shigemura Research Lab.
Your students included Akihiko
Kayaba and Nobuyuki Sugou.
So I know what I'm about
to show you will interest you.
(GRUNTS)
Kikuoka, what is that?
Welcome to Rath.