Wait a minute. Am I dreaming?
We're in Japan, right?
And Japan's not really known
for its tropical locales.
Behold, Haruhi! Bask in
the beauty of tropical birds!
Aren't they breathtaking?
I wonder what they're called.
Um, where was the exit, again?
Try to make the most of this
downtime and just relax.
We're so worried about keeping
our good looks day and night.
We deserve a little vacation.
Personally, I think this is
pointless and a waste of time,
so can I go home?
I should really be studying
and I've got a ton of laundry
to do today.
Hey senpai,
where are we, anyway?
Target.
Captured!
Wait! What the?!
Good work.
Now take her with you.
Roger!
Hold on. Where are we going?!
This place is a brand new
theme park that my family,
the Otori Group,
runs. It's called
the "Tropical Aqua Garden".
I don't understand. I thought
the Otori group ran hospitals,
and that they're focused
on the medical business,
Kyoya-senpai.
Yes, but my family likes
to diversify and try
different things. Besides,
this place could be classified
as a healing facility.
It's therapeutic. Think
of all the people who are
over worked that would love a
vacation in the south tropics.
However, they may not
be able to get the time off
or they may not
be able to afford it.
Those people can now seek
refuge here at this theme park
and reduce their stress levels.
The Otori group's primary
concern has always been
for the good health
and well-being
of the general public.
It sounds suspicious to me.
The park doesn't officially
open until next month,
but the Host Club was given
a special advance invitation.
This is so relaxing.
We don't have to worry about
keeping all of our guests
entertained for once.
It's truly like a holiday
for handsome young soldiers.
I guess that's
what you'd call it.
Jungle Pool SOS!
Haru-chan! Wanna share
some coconut juice with me?
Or do you wanna try
a piece of the mango cake?
Yeah, sure. I'll have
some coconut juice with you.
Hah!
Haruhi. You wanna go
check out the water slide?
Hang on. What's the deal
with that pullover
you're wearing?
Oh, this thing?
Here. Do what
you've got to do.
Okay We'll do what we can.
Miss Fujioka, just follow me.
But why?
Hold on! What're you doing?!
Hey! Stop that!
We've been asked to help
you choose a swimsuit!
We've brought all of our
mother's latest designs for you
to choose from.
Just pick whichever
one you want.
Are you ready, Miss Fujioka?
It's time to pick one!
Thanks, but I don't
need a swimsuit.
Why don't you let me
select one for you?
No, not that one.
I don't want a bikini.
But you would look
so good in this one.
No, wait! I bet
this one would be cute!
But that's nothing more
than a couple of strings!
Senpai?
Just hurry up and put it on.
A proper young woman
should not show that much skin
until after she's married.
So, you're not going to swim?
Hold on, you do swim,
don't you?
I can swim just as good as
the next guy but this isn't
my idea of fun. I'm not
that big on water parks;
we're just gonna spend
all day goofing off.
Honestly, I'd
rather be at home.
I don't understand what's so
great about this place, anyway?
I mean, all you really need
to play in the water
is a plastic pool.
A plastic pool- what is that?
Let's see. I guess they're
about this big, round,
and to use it you have
to pump it full of air.
You dunce.
That's an inflatable
boat, dummy
There's no way something that
small could be used as a pool.
Yeah.
It's a small pool! Haven't
you ever seen little kids
playing in one of them?
You idiots! If Haruhi thinks
it's a pool then it's a pool,
got it? Don't go
embarrassing her.
She can't help that
she's an ignorant commoner.
So are we supposed to lie
to her- is that what you want?
I can't help but feel like
I should be offended
by that comment.
Never mind that, we've
got a question for ya.
Why did you make Haruhi put
on that yellow monstrosity?
I would've thought for sure
that'd you be all-
I want to see Haruhi
in a swimsuit!
-Not making her
cover-up like that.
It was surprising.
I know what he's up to.
He made Haruhi cover-up
because he didn't want
anyone else to see her
in a bathing suit.
Do you really think that's it?
He must be one of those
jealous, pervert types.
That's pretty twisted.
That's not it at all!
I was just trying to protect
her innocence as any
father or guardian would.
After all, even if she is
wearing a swimsuit, it is not
decent for a lady to walk around
half-naked in front of boys.
Haru-chan! Let's play!
You wanna go swimming
in the current pool with me?
Nah. I'm not gonna
swim today. Hold on.
You know how to swim;
you still need that float?
Just looks cuter this way,
you know?
You're right. Those bunnies
are pretty cute.
He's so innocent.
No way! You've
got it all wrong!
Is that Renge?
How does she do that?
It's like the rig follows us.
That outfit's pretty
impressive.
What's with the tattoo
on your stomach?
Oh that? You don't recognize it?
I'm cosplaying.
Yeah? As who?
La-la.
LaLa? Like the
manga magazine?
Her petite and slender frame,
her blue eyes that light up
young men's faces,
her singing voice!
I am Quon Kisaragi!
I wouldn't have guessed.
I had no idea who
you were supposed to be.
Hey boss, are you sure it's
okay for Renge to be dressed-
-like that.
Well yeah, that's okay.
And why is that?
Because it's cosplay? I guess.
Listen up, boys!
You obviously need help
understanding Haninozuka's
hidden motives! Look!
Takashi!
What are you talking about?
Think about what
he said to you earlier.
Just looks cuter
this way, you know?
He's not being as sweet
and innocent as you think.
I agree. Try putting the
word 'I' at the beginning
of that sentence.
Just looks cuter
this way, you know?
I look cute!
He planned that?!
That's Haninozuka for you.
In the last episode,
he felt threatened by
another loli-boy type
so he's taken steps
to keep his rank.
I should give him more credit.
He's a lot smarter
than I thought.
Hey! Look at this,
everybody!
Check it out! Look! Even though
we're swimming really fast
we never go any farther
than we are now!
So, what's up with him?
Could he really be that smart?
I got ya!
C'mon, boss, let's go!
Let's have a water gun fight.
It'll be me and
Kaoru against you.
If you get it in the face,
you lose. What do you say?
Forget it.
Why would I want
to subject myself
to a childish game like that?
Haruhi, I think it's time
that we got married!
Then we'll honeymoon in Atami!
Do you really think I'd ever
let Haruhi marry you guys?!
Daddy says no!
Taking a break, huh?
Want something to drink?
Yeah, thanks.
I'll get you guys!
Sideways-leaping shot!
That's cheating!
Honey-senpai!
Mitsukuni!
Mori-senpai.
Gentlemen, we're
going after Honey-senpai!
That pool looks
like the quickest way!
Charge!
Wait! I wouldn't go-
There are alligators in there!
Okay. So we can't use that pool,
then let's try this way next!
They're here, too!
And here!
What's with all
the alligators?
Beats me.
Those alligators belong to the
park's tropical animals exhibit.
I guess it is kind of dangerous
to let them run wild.
Though, the cause of our present
situation seems to be
the location of the switch
for the current pool.
I'll have to have a little chat
with our designers.
Thanks a lot, you guys.
I got some great data today.
You what?!
This is a map of the
Tropical Aqua Garden.
This is our current location.
We need to get here -
I have a feeling that's where
Honey-senpai probably ended up.
It might be tough because to get
there we'll have to make it
through this jungle area
in the southern block.
Distance wise, we're
talking about 800 meters.
It looks like there's a lot
of undeveloped areas.
Any idea what might be lurking
in those parts of the jungle?
Since they're still
being developed,
I'm afraid I don't know.
Whatever's out there could be
even more dangerous-
-than alligators.
All right. Now, this is
a mission of survival!
I know we can make it
through the treacherous jungle
in one piece... It is our sworn
duty to save Honey-senpai!
Wow, this place is just
like a real jungle, huh?
Yeah and I keep
hearing all of these
really strange animal calls.
You don't think that
all those animal sounds-
-could belong to
the real thing, do you?
To be honest I'm not sure,
but I do know that my family
always strives for authenticity
whatever the cost.
Mori-senpai is always
so straight-faced.
I can never tell what he's
thinking, but even though
he's doing a good job of staying
calm, I'm sure he's worried-
Mori-senpai is-
-acting as clumsy
as you do, Boss.
Shut up!
Just as I thought,
he is worried.
Uh-oh, it's about time
for the squall.
Huh?
Hey, Mori-senpai. You seem to be
really close with Honey-senpai.
Are the two of you
like childhood friends?
You mean, you don't know-
-that they're cousins?.
You're kidding me?
They're related?
The Morinozukas have been
serving the Haninozuka family
for generations.
However, two generations ago,
the families became relatives
by marriage and the
master-servant relationship
soon became a thing
of the past.
But even so, Mori-senpai
has always made a point
to accompany
Honey-senpai.
It must really
get his blood going.
The blood of a loyal servant
flows like a mighty river
through Mori-senpai's veins.
Such a beautiful
story! I'm touched!
I don't know if I'd
call it a beautiful story.
I'm not sure I understand all
this blood and loyalty business.
But it's obvious that
Mori-senpai thinks an awful lot
of Honey-senpai.
Hey Mori-senpai,
it's gonna be all right.
I'm sure that Honey-senpai
is safe. He's a lot tougher
than you might think he is,
and if he gets hungry
the trees are full of bananas.
Bananas?
What's he going to say?
You're right.
Don't tell me Mori-senpai's out
for my spot as Haruhi's daddy?!
Nobody wants that
spot but you, boss.
That's kinda creepy
when you think about it.
What?! Who are you
calling creepy?!
Hello? It's me. Well,
we've had an incident that's
caused some trouble.
Ha! You're a big ole perv!
Shut up! I'm not a perv!
Mori-senpai, you're
going the wrong way!
Honey-senpai was headed
in the opposite direction!
You're wrong.
He went this way.
Hey, wait up! It's too
dangerous to go alone!
I'm coming with you!
Haruhi.
That's the first time he's
ever called me by name.
Yes, at once, please.
Senpai's a perv for Haruhi!
Would you jerks quit
calling me a perv!...
My family's private police
force is going to send in
a search and rescue team
to help us.
They're better equipped to
find Honey senpai than we are.
So let's just go back to
the gate and wait there.
Shut up before
I beat your faces in!
Hey where are Mori and Haruhi?
Immediate emergency
mobilization order!
I repeat, immediate emergency
Master Kyoya's friend has gone
missing near the wave pool.
Our search target is a small
young man. Orders are to
eliminate any suspicious
figures- show them no mercy.
Repeat, eliminate any suspicious
Target confirmed.
The target has been captured
by a suspicious man.
We'll take the target
into custody.
You know, I don't believe I
mentioned to them that there
are other visitors here
Huh. Oh, well.
You there! Put the boy
down immediately!
If you refuse we'll
remove him forcefully!
Hold on!
The suspect is resisting!
Prepare to fire warning shots!
Takashi! Haru-chan!
Outta the way!
Hey! What do you think
you're doing, pipsqueak?!
Whoa.
You guys should be more
careful who you mess with!
Picking on my friends
is bad! Got it?
Haruhi!
Haruhi! Are you all right?!
Hey! It's Tama-chan!
Oh Wow.
You okay, senpai?
Haruhi!
I was worried about you.
I'm not sure what happened here
but at least
they're still alive.
It's pretty amazing that this
is Honey-senpai's work.
He must have really
been holding back.
What do you mean
he was holding back?
So then-
-you don't know about Senpai?!
The Haninozukas are famous
for their martial arts.
Not only have they helped train
the police and SDF forces
but they've also worked
with several overseas
military forces.
Honey-senpai in particular
has been called
the dreadnaught of the
Haninozuka family.
By the time he was in middle
school he'd become the
national champion in
both karate and judo.
Mori-senpai's no slouch
either. He won the national
championship in kendo
when he was just
in middle school.
So how were you able
to find us, Honey-senpai?
It wasn't hard. It didn't
take me long to reach
the end of the current pool, so
I decided to look for you guys.
We humbly apologize!
I am a 2nd-generation student
of the Ishizuka Dojo!
I'm a student of
the Todoroki Dojo!
And I'm from the Otakeh Dojo!
We are in your debt!
Why? Is something wrong?
Yes, sir! We're so sorry, sir!
We were unaware that
we were searching
for Mitsukuni Haninozuka!
We've committed
a terrible offense here!
I apologize for this
confrontation. But my dojo
will be so excited to hear that
I've come face to face with
the great Hahninozuka!
I cherish this moment!
So he is smart; he's deeper
than I could have imagined!
Takashi, you did an amazing
job of protecting Haru-chan.
I bet you were pretty lonely
without me around, huh?
I don't know
if I'd say that.
You know, maybe we should
go to the beach next.
Yeah, the beach would be nice.
You idiots,
Haruhi's not interested
in anything like that.
Actually, I might like
to go to the beach.
I may not be into this silly
water park but I like the ocean.
It would be nice to go to the
beach, and It's so pretty.
Yeah! All right. Then that's
where we'll go next time!
We're all gonna go to
the beach, Tama-chan?
That'll be fun,
don't you think?
Yeah.
We come to the beach
like she wanted and
all of a sudden Haruhi
and I get into a big fight!
I thought you weren't gonna
talk to me anymore, senpai.
Haruhi!
Next time, "The Sun,
the Sea, and the Host Club!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll See you then!