Oh, And those go in the central
building's main salon, okay?
Alright.
Hey, be careful with that.
Uh. Aren't school fairs meant,
to be, I don't know,
more about students
proudly showcasing
unique things that
they've made by hand?
Perhaps for a mere
average school, yes.
But at Ouran, the emphasis
is on planning and
leadership skills.
Keep in mind, most of
our students are being
groomed into positions of
leadership, so they're
required to showcase a
talent for upward mobility
not arts-and-crafts.
Whoa, whoa.
Nicely done. You handle
the reigns like a pro.
Haru-chan!
Climb on board.
We're rehearsing for the
big Ouran Fair parade.
Oh wow, it's right
out of a fairy tale!
How romantic!
Can we have a ride too?
Hey, you know, you've
gotten pretty good at this.
There's nothing to it,
you should've practiced
with me earlier.
Well, just because we're
twins doesn't make both
of us good drivers.
It's kinda neat having all
of us together like this
for a carriage ride, huh?
Yeah, whatever.
Oh, and for the actual parade
tomorrow we'll all be
in 18th century
French costumes.
Your outfit will be
especially opulent, Haruhi.
Oh, wonderful.
Ah. The fair's opening
ceremony has started.
Let's make this fair,
the best one yet!
Sounds good to me.
"The Host Club
Declares Dissolution."
Now remember, as part of
the fair, the Host Club
will be open to
parents and vistors
for the next two days, which
means we will need to be
even more charming than
usual. Let's get out there
and show our honored guests
the time of their lives!
Isn't it just wonderful,
mother? This is the
Host Club I've been telling
you so much about.
What do you think?
Well actually. I cannot
say I approve of this.
I think that these
young men just enjoy
being fawned over.
You are quite right, madam.
We are such shameless,
selfish creatures.
All of this is mere pretense--
--for spending time
with lovely young ladies
such as yourself. It is
a weakness. Forgive me.
Oh!
What an enchanting club!
I told you!
You're too kind, both of you.
Good grief.
Here, your buttons are
mismatched. Allow me.
Thank you very much.
How adorable!
They must be brothers.
The older one is so thoughtful.
Wrong.
But you see,
our mother and father,
were both so busy. That they
had no time for the two of us.
We played by ourselves.
Which is the reason
we're so lonely now.
Oh, you poor things!
You have got to be kidding me.
One of our daily goals here
at the Host Club is
to evoke different time periods.
So we make it a point
to thoroughly research
a wide variety of historical
traditions in the interest of
maintaining authenticity.
That's quite impressive!
Yeah, quite
impressively political.
This is a bit too much
even by our standards.
You could buy
a small country with all
the money we're wasting.
What nonsense! That's not
the Host Club way
at all and you know it!
Happiness is above
any price tag! Besides, think
of all the exposure! We'll --
No, Haruhi's right, you have
overshot the budget.
Kyoya.
The use of this salon
notwithstanding, you had
a period-style carriage shipped
in all the way from France.
Must you always be so
capricious? Your impulsiveness
overwhelms my
accounting skills.
Typical.
Whatever! Capricious is just
another word for creative!
I'll have you know
the whims of the
Host Club King
are the stuff of dreams,
no price is too high!
Welcome.
Can I get anything for you?
Maybe something sweet?
You're with the Host Club?
Yes.
Father!
Do not refer to me as father.
The term is far too familiar.
You will address me
properly as Chairman.
Ah very good! welcome sir.
Please, let me
show you to your seat.
Thank you.
Kyoya, my boy, if not for
your being here I'm sure
this club would
be a shambles.
My son must give you
no end of trouble.
Oh, on the contrary, sir.
Your son's vision is what
keeps us viable.
May I bring you anything?
Yes, yes. Of course.
Haruhi, you're needed.
What?!
So you're Haruhi Fujioka.
Come, sit with me.
Alright, thank you sir.
So this guy is Tamaki-senpai
father? Funny, they don't
look all that much alike.
Nice to meet you Chairman.
I was just thinking earlier
that I ought to have paid
my respects to you
a long time ago.
I'm so sorry.
You know, "Chairman" is so dry.
Why don't you call me, yes.
Call me your uncle.
It would please me.
Wow. I guess the apple doesn't
fall far from the tree
after all.
I find I'm just so busy lately
that I'm seldom here in person.
But I've certainly heard some
wonderful things about you.
Oh, why. thank you, sir.
If ever you find yourself
in trouble, I want you to know
that you can come to
your uncle for anything.
'Kay.
Father!
Chairman!
What do you think you're doing?!
Remove your hands
at once, please!
Kyoya-senpai!
Is this how my son has
been wasting his time?
That's Kyo-chan's
father isn't it?
Yes.
You are an embarrassment
to the Ootori name.
Suou, my friend. I am sorry
you had to witness that.
That did seem rather harsh,
given how exceptional
he really is.
For a man with three fine
young sons to carry on
his legacy, your avarice
would seem to run deep.
I've heard about your
trouble. Believe me,
It's only a matter of
time before the media
gets wind of it. Please tell
me you're not taking
that out on your son.
Kyoya, are you alright?
Your dad is so mean!
You should never, ever hit
someone who's wearing glasses!
I don't think
it's really about that.
He wasn't upset with you 'cause
of the Host Club was he?
Don't worry about it.
It's not like I haven't
been expecting this.
Because of the host club?
Whims have
consequences, Tamaki.
Take my word for it,
they do not come cheaply
for people like us.
Accept it. Life is hard.
It's time for you to grow up
and realize that dreaming
only postpones the inevitable.
Haruhi!
Coming!
Thank you all so much
for taking time out of
your busy schedule
to visit us today.
Start thinking about
the future, son.
If you plan on becoming
head of the Suou family
there's a long,
hard road ahead of you.
You're going to have to live
with the choices you make
for the rest of your life.
I advise you to think very
carefully about what it is
you really want before
it's too late.
Now look sharp.
Your grandmother is here.
Grandmother! I'm so
glad you could come!
Aw, that's so sweet. So that's
Tamaki-senpai's grandmother.
I hate that woman.
Please come in, take a seat.
Don't patronize me.
Filthy Child
Lady Éclair, come over here
for a moment please.
Hey, I was just.
What?
For the remainder of
the day and tomorrow,
you will be Lady Éclair's
personal escort.
What's wrong?
I gave you an order.
Hello there, Tamaki.
Very well, grandmother.
I will do everything in my power
to ensure her happiness.
Just as you wish.
Tama-chan isn't
coming back, is he?
So does he really
plan to spend-
-the entire fair
escorting some stranger?
Come my princess.
Let us be off.
Éclair , right?
Or something like that.
Who is she to him?
That's the mystery.
I could tell you.
Oh, Renge?
Éclair, Tonnerre, She's
the youngest daughter of
the renowned French
Tonnerre family.
They descend from royalty.
Indeed, the family has quite
a history. Their wealth is
something of a legend among
financial heavyweights.
In fact, just being associated
with them makes you part
of a very elite group.
They also own Grand Tonnerre,
a firm that's been
buying up a lot of business
in Japan lately.
Of course that doesn't
explain why Lady Éclair
has come here
to visit Tamaki.
Isn't this charming?
A picturesque gondola ride
and artists'
showcase all in one.
Everything you see here,
was created by members
of the Ouran Art Club.
How pedestrian.
Clearly the work of novices.
That was a bit harsh.
What would you have me do?
The students put a lot of
hard work into these pieces.
But we can go somewhere else
if you like, my lady.
Tamaki.
I would like to hear
you play the piano.
For me?
Of course that doesn't
explain why Lady Éclair's
has come to visit Tamaki.
In here?
Well, it is
a music room after all.
So this is the room
where you and that precious
little Host Club of yours
hold court, is it?
I must admit it was
impressive seeing you all
in action earlier.
You must be very close.
Naturally. You know
what they say,
"the family that plays
together stays together."
Family? What a sentimental
notion. I believe here in Japan
they refer to that
as "playing house."
You're so whimsical, Tamaki.
I'll bet they all fall
over themselves trying
to keep up with you.
Especially that one
in the glasses.
The one who got
slapped by his father.
Must you always be so
capricious , your impulsiveness
overwhelms my accounting skills.
Could that be true?
Is everyone making sacrifices
just to keep me happy?
Haruhi could be much closer
to becoming a lawyer
right now if I hadn't forced
her be part of this club.
She came here to study, but I've
completely monopolized all her
free time.
Who is it?
Oh, Haruhi. What are you doing?
I just came back
to change outfits.
You were the one who wanted us
to change costumes at least
three times a day.
Look, Everyone's upset
with you for disappearing
on us like that.
You should be with your club.
My apologies, I'm afraid
he belongs to me
for the time being.
Forgive me for asking, but do
I detect a hint of jealousy?
Oh Haruhi!
So Is it true?! Is it true?!
You're actually jealous?!
Sorry, but no. I guess
I'll be be leaving now.
Some of us have work to do.
Hey, wait a second! Haruhi!
Please. You can't possibly be
interested in a shrew like that.
My lady!
I would appreciate it if
you would not refer to
my little girl as a shrew.
Your little girl?
They're not
a real family, Tamaki.
So stop playing house.
What are you doing?!
Wouldn't you prefer
the real thing?
Because I can give it
to you, you know.
How dashing!
Oh my!
Haru-chan looks great!
She does.
Not bad.
So where did the boss go?
He was looking forward
to this the most.
Our King is lounging
in Music Room 3.
He's "entertaining"
Lady Éclair.
Well, well, well.
It sounds like someone's
a little jealous.
Like I said. I'm not.
Like you said?
Look I. I just think he's
being even more irresponsible
than usual today.
You said it yourself,
Kyoya. He's impulsive.
True, he certainly is.
But in this instance he's
obeying the whims
of his grandmother.
Please come in,
take a seat.
Don't patronize me.
Filthy child.
Um, You know, now that
I think about it,
Tamaki's grandmother seemed
really cold towards him earlier.
Is there some special
reason for that?
Well, everyone else
knows about it.
See, Tamaki-senpai
is illegitimate.
Twenty some-odd years ago,
the Suou Family patriarch
died at a young age.
For political reasons,
Chairman Yuzuru was rushed
into a marriage at
the behest of his mother
to a woman of her own choosing.
That's how he became
head of the family.
But several years later,
the chairman fell passionately
in love with a beautiful
young woman he met in Paris.
Not long after,
Tama-chan was born.
No Mother. I am leaving my
wife. I'm going to marry her.
The boss' grandmother
vehemently objected.
Because of her poor health,
living in Japan proved too
difficult for senpai's mother,
and so she raised him in France
until he was fourteen.
His childhood seems
to have been a happy one.
But as time wore on, the family
business on his mother's side
went belly up, and when they
were forced into debt.
The boss' grandmother,
worried about there being
no heir to carry on
the family name,
came up with a proposal.
I will provide you with
the means to live comfortably
for the rest of your days.
In exchange, Tahmaki is to come
and live with me in Japan.
Without You.
All contact between the two
of you will be prohibited,
forever. These conditions
are non-negotiable.
Wow.
The current patriarch may
be Chairman Yuzuru Suou
technically but for the time
being, all the family's assets
remain under the control
of Tamaki's grandmother.
What's more with his
mother's health being so frail.
Tamaki understood the grim
prospects facing her if she
were left to live in debt.
So.
I've decided. I'm going
to go to Japan,
It's all for the best.
Just promise me, mom.
Promise me you'll take care.
Not long afterward either out
of anguish or just plain guilt
over having bartered her son
away for financial security.
Tamaki's mother left France in
shame and went into hiding.
Her current
whereabouts are unknown.
To this day he's
never seen her again.
Not once.
So. I won't get to see
mommy anymore?
I had no idea. He always
seems so cheerful.
Who would have ever guessed?
If I were in senpai's shoes, I
don't know that I could ever
forgive my grandmother
for something like that.
It's easy to feel sorry for him.
But the hardships that
he endured as a child helped
mold him into the
person he is today.
He'll be fine.
The Host Club is his refuge,
which means when all
is said and done.
He still has us.
Tama-chan!
Everyone, I have an
important announcement.
As of today, Lady Éclair
Tonnerre and I are
officially engaged.
Futhermore, the Host Club
will be permanently
dissolved after the Ouran Fair.
That is all.
To be honest, I used to think
you were the strangest bunch
of misfits and loonies
I'd ever met.
I mean, serving as hosts
in an after-school club?
Next time, the final episode:
"This is Our Ouran Fair."
All of you, I...