I'm never gonna hear the
end of it if I show up late.
What's this? Where am I?
Welcome!
When I opened the door,
the whole place was decked
out like a tropical paradise.
Can you see this
from Heaven, Mom?
This is the club
I was forced to join.
"The Job of
a High School Host"
You finally made it,
Haruhi. You're so late.
I could be wrong but
my calendar says it's still
early spring.
Huddling under a kotatsu
table fearing the cold
is nonsense!
And besides the heating
system we have is the best.
Do you have a problem
with the way we run our club,
Haruhi? Be careful
what you say.
You owe us eight million
yen, remember?
Gentlemen don't bundle up
in bulky clothing.
It may be chilly, early spring
out there in the real world,
but here at the club
we want to surprise our
chilly little kittens with
a warm, tropical paradise.
Oh yes! We've turned
this place into nirvana.
A balmy, tropical island
of everlasting summer!
That's funny cause I feel
a massive chill right now.
Only those with excellent
social standing and those
from filthy rich families
are lucky enough to
spend their time here
at the elite, private school,
Ouran Academy.
The Ouran Host Club
is where the school's
handsomest boys, with too
much time on their hands,
entertain young ladies who
also have way too much time
on their hands. Just think
of it as Ouran Academy's
elegant playground for the
super-rich and beautiful.
What heartlessness!
Even with my lustrous skin,
shining like brilliant
ivory exposed by
my Balinese King outfit--
I'm no more than
a slave before my goddess.
I kneel before you
and swear my loyalty.
Tamaki.
Lucky.
Oh wow.
Oh yes, I almost forgot
to mention to you ladies.
Next week the Ouran Host Club
is sponsoring a party.
We're throwing a party?
What kind of party
is it going to be?
Is it going to be formal?
Yes, in fact, we've rented
the school's largest hall.
It's the perfect place
for dancing.
But I really wanted to spend
some alone time with you, Kaoru.
Don't be upset Hikaru.
I know exactly how you feel.
Oh wow! They're so sexy hot!
I can't believe it.
Oh my gosh.
The guests seem to be
even more worked up
than they usually are.
Showing some skin proves
popular with the ladies.
So, are you the one
who came up with this
tropical paradise idea?
I have no decision
making authority.
All of the club's policies
have been laid out
by the club's
king, Tamaki.
But, I guess there's
no harm in admitting
to casually slipping a Bali
photo book onto his desk.
So, he's the real brains
behind the operation.
Ta-da!
Oh you're so cute, Honey!
Hi ladies. I love these
Balinese flowers.
We had them flown in. Takashi!
There! Now we match!
They're covered in camellias!
I'm still thoroughly confused
by the two of them.
Um, Haruhi?
Aren't you going to wear
a tropical outfit like
the other boys?
I'd like to see that.
Well, no I, I just don't
think it's appropriate
to wear anything but early
spring attire in early spring,
you know?
But we have one ready
for you Haruhi!
I think you'll like it.
You and I are a pair!
No thanks.
Wow Haruhi.
You're really faithful to the
different seasons, aren't you?
I think that's great!
I hope we're lucky enough
that the cherry blossoms are
in full bloom on
the night of the party.
The two of us, dancing
among the cherry blossoms.
It's so dreamy.
You really think so?
You know ladies,
I think it's so cute when
you dream like that.
Excuse me.
I hate to disturb but
I think it's time for
the hosts to
switch clients.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You must be my next
appointment, Miss--?
My name's Kanako.
Kanako Kasugazaki.
You're even cuter
than I expected.
I've decided from now
on you're going to be
my new favorite host, Haruhi.
I can't take this anymore.
Hey boss, why don't you stop
eating that commoner's ramen
and come over here to help
us with the party planning.
Does it really bother you
that Princess Kasuga
has taken a liking to Haruhi?
He shouldn't be surprised.
She's had the illness for
a while now, hasn't she?
What illness?
She's got the
host-hopping disease.
AKA the never-the-same-boy
-twice disease.
Usually our customers
choose a favorite host
and then see them regularly.
However, Princess Kanako
tends to change her favorites
on a regular basis.
That's right!
Cause before she chose you
she was with Tama-chan!
Oh, so he's upset because
I took her from him.
Shut up! I couldn't care less!
I'm running out
of patience! Haruhi.
It's time you started
dressing like a girl!
I don't understand how you
could be so popular with
the ladies when
you yourself are a lady!
No one in the entire school
knows the truth except
for those of us here.
Yeah, she opted out
of taking gym classes.
And the attendance numbers
are all mixed together up,
so no one can tell.
That's enough Haruhi.
Now you listen to Daddy.
Daddy wants you to go back
to the way you were!
Don't go blowing up my photos
without asking me first!
The more I look at this
picture the more amazed I am.
How could this possibly
become that?
The day before school
started one of the kids
in my neighborhood
got some gum in my hair.
It's a real pain to get gum
out of long hair so
I decided to cut it all off.
I didn't care if I looked
like a dude, you know?
A girl should never refer
to herself as a "dude'!
Momma! Haruhi's using those
dirty boy words again!
I'm sorry, but who is "Momma"?
Based on club position,
I assume it's me.
Look, I don't see what
you're crying about.
Working as a host I can pay
back more of my debt.
It'll never happen if I'm
just an errand boy.
Hate to change the subject
but do you have
formal dancing experience?
You'll need it at the party.
No but the party doesn't
have anything to do
with my quota, right? I'm not
interested in going to events
so if I could be excused--
Definitely not.
A refined gentleman
must know how to dance.
If you want to live the life
of a host that badly,
you're going to have to
show us how far
you're willing to go, Haruhi.
I order you to master dancing
the waltz in one week
and you will demonstrate it
for us at the party or
I'll tell the entire
school that you're a girl
and knock you back
down to errand boy.
Quick, quick, slow.
Good work, Haruhi.
Now on the "slow" you should
bring your feet together.
Remember the gentleman
always leads and make sure
to look at the lady
you're dancing with.
Got it.
I'm so sorry,
Miss Kasugazaki!
It's okay, Haruhi.
Can I help you up? Like this?
Why so gloomy, boss?
I bet it's because
he wanted to be the one
Haruhi practices with.
I think you may be right
but he's way too tall
to stand in as a woman.
Thank you so much for allowing
me to practice with you.
I really appreciate it.
Oh, no problem. I heard
that you're not seeing
any customers today so that
you can practice dancing.
I'm glad I got to spend
this time alone with you.
Oh my! This is a new tea
set, isn't it? It's Ginori.
Jinori?
You have a keen eye,
mademoiselle.
In fact, we just received
them yesterday.
We decided that it was
about time for the club
to upgrade its tea sets.
I see. What a
pretty color. Lovely.
You must really be
into tableware, huh?
Not really. I mean,
no, of course I'm not.
What ever would give you
that idea?
She obviously knows
a lot about it.
Why would she lie?
Hello! I'm here to deliver
with the new teacups
you ordered.
Thank you very much.
Every item that you've
chosen for us has been
extremely popular with the
ladies. I'm quite impressed.
Well, that's good to hear.
So, do you sell tea sets?
No, I'm just a regular student.
Can't you tell by the uniform?
Oh, Haruhi. You're so funny.
I can't blame you
for not knowing.
After all, he doesn't
really look like an heir to
a first class company.
First class company?
His family's business, the
Suzushima Trading Company,
deals primarily in the
importing of tableware.
They currently have the top
market share in the country.
Wow.
So whenever something
exceptional comes in
we've asked him
to send it our way.
He has a great eye for fine
china. Don't you, Suzushima?
You think? I've still got
a lot to learn but thank you.
Aren't you leaving next month
to study abroad in England?
Yes, I am. Well,
I'd better go now.
So are you enjoying
the Host Club?
I get the feeling you and
that guy are kinda close.
Don't be ridiculous!
We hardly know each other!
What makes you
say that, Haruhi?
Now if you'll please
excuse me. Take care.
Haru-chan! Guess what?
They do know each other!
Suzushima is
Kasuga-chan's fiancé.
Kyoya, how long have
you known about this?
About the two of them
being engaged?
Well, as you know
I conduct general searches
on all of our customers.
The two of them were
childhood friends.
It seems that their engagement
was arranged by their parents.
I didn't think the
information would benefit us
so I disregarded it.
I see.
Toru Suzushima: Outstanding
grades, fair social status.
He's ordinary looking,
but he's reliable.
If I had to fault him
for anything--
He doesn't have
much presence.
And he's faint hearted.
So in other words, he's boring.
I had no idea they were so
merciless toward other guys.
Suzushima is a good boy. Right?
Yeah.
All right, everyone.
We'll have to work
on our strategy.
Which one?
Men, it is our responsibility
as members of
the elite Ouran Host Club
to make every girl happy!
It is so good to see you here
tonight, my little lambs.
The Ouran Host Club
would like to bid you--
Welcome.
As always, ladies, the Host
Club Members are here
for your entertainment.
So, we invite you to dance
to your heart's content.
Based on her dancing skills,
one lucky young lady
will be chosen as
tonight's queen.
The queen's reward will be a
passionate kiss on the cheek
from our King.
Well, good luck to you,
my darlings.
Haruhi, show some enthusiasm.
Well excuse me, you guys.
Sorry, I'm not used to this
sort of thing. I've only
ever gone to the festivals
in my neighborhood park.
I don't know if you can really
consider that a party or not.
Well since you're already here
you might as well get yourself
something to eat.
We've got quite a spread.
A spread? With fancy tuna?
Fan-
-cy
Tuna?
Get some fancy tuna
here right now!
Add some deluxe sushi.
Damn these filthy rich jerks.
Uh.
Hello Haruhi, I've been
looking all over for you.
Do you think maybe I could
have the next dance?
Yeah, of course you can.
Kasuga-chan is here.
Alright men, then let us
commence with our operation.
Roger!
What? Kidnapped?
There she is!
You didn't have
to be so forceful.
Never mind that.
Go get changed.
A little "accident" towards
the end of the night would be
quite thrilling.
And remember Haruhi, there
are only 20 minutes remaining
before the party
reaches its climax.
Suzushima is already
waiting for you
in the classroom
across the hall.
You have to ask him
how he feels, okay?
Uh, we know this is
the boss's strategy but
it's kind of unsettling.
Gentlemen. Here you all are.
What are you doing?
The guests are waiting for--
So, what do you think?
Wow, you look so cute!
My face feels heavy and it's
hard to walk in these shoes.
Good luck, Haruhi!
I can't believe
she's so pretty.
You're the one
who wrote this letter?
You're totally different
from what I imagined.
Letter?
"I'm in love-love! From
the first time I saw you
I've been head over
heels in love!"
"It's like my heart is stuck
in a never ending typhoon.
All these feelings of love keep
whipping around in my heart,
like the breaking waves! When
the typhoon's rising waters
come I want to rendezvous with
you on Noah's Ark! I do! I do!"
Who wrote such
a stupid letter?
'Scuze me. Have we met
somewhere before?
No! This is the first time
I've ever talked to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm flattered by your letter
but I'm afraid I don't
feel the same way.
You see, another girl
already has my heart.
Oh, well I didn't know
that you had a girlfriend.
Unfortunately,
she's not my girlfriend.
In fact, I think she's
completely over me.
In all honesty, she'd be
happier with someone
more self-confident than me.
Where exactly are you
taking me, Tamaki?
You know.
You're not the kind
of girl who's good at
manipulating others.
What do you mean by that?
I have you figured out, Kanako.
I know you're switching
from host to host to get his
attention and I've noticed
that you always look the
happiest gazing into a tea cup.
Hey! Check these out, Kanako.
So pretty!
There's a Wedgewood,
a Foley, Worcester.
Over here's a Ginori
and a Meissen.
Someday you're gonna be
my wife, Kanako,
so I'll tell you about
all of 'em, 'kay?
It's pointless. It doesn't
matter how hard I try,
he never notices me.
And now he's decided
to study abroad
without--without even
telling me.
That's why I decided
I need to change.
I want to see the world and
hopefully, become a better man.
I know it's selfish but I
wonder if she'll wait for me.
Yeah, you're right. That
is pretty selfish of you.
But maybe she would wait.
You'll never know if you
don't tell her how you feel.
You obviously have strong
feelings for her so why not
go ahead and talk to her?
I think once you decide to
change then you've already
began your
transformation.
Kanako.
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to
interrupt you two, I just--
Kanako!
Looks like we just
made matters worse.
But he did go
running after her.
It's our responsibility,
as members of
the elite Ouran Host Club,
to make every girl happy.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It is now time for us to
begin the final dance of
this evening's festivities.
The last waltz of the
night has been chosen by
the host club for this couple.
Princess Kasuga?
May I have this dance?
Yes.
I love you, Kanako.
I've always loved you and
I want you to be my wife.
Tonight marks the end
of my host hopping.
May this awkward couple
be forever blessed!
And now we'll announce
the queen of the ball.
Congratulations Princess
Kanako Kasugazaki!
And for her reward, a kiss
on the cheek from the king!
You ready?
Haruhi Fujioka will stand
in for Tamaki!
Kyoya did say that a little
"accident" towards the end
of the night might make
the evening more thrilling
for everyone!
It's just on the cheek, right?
You should accept it.
It will commemorate your
graduation from host-hopping.
There's no way I can kiss her.
If you do it we'll cut
your debt by one-third.
Well it is just a peck
on the cheek.
Hey! You don't think this
is Haru-chan's first kiss,
do you?
What?
Wait Haruhi!
I never would've
thought that I'd end up
giving my first kiss
to another girl.
But it was such
an amazing night.
So I guess it's just as well.
If word gets out that I'm
really a girl I won't be able
to stay in the Host Club.
Don't you worry, Haruhi.
I will protect
your secret no matter what!
Next time, "Beware
the Physical Exam!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!