Hey, you okay?
I'm sorry about--
Get out!
Ma.
Ma!
"Tamaki's Unwitting
Depression."
Uh. My bad.
Peeping Tom!
You saw--
--didn't you, Bossa Nova?
No. I didn't see! I mean,
I caught a glance, yeah,
but it was all
so fast that I didn't-
It was just an accident!
I swear to you
that I am not a pervert!
Of course you would say that.
Sure sign of
a guilty conscience.
How is it that the lovely
item is the scariest person
in the room?
So then Fujioka's a girl?
Red alert. He's on to
Haruhi's little secret.
That's not good.
So let's hear it.
How much of her maidenly
terra incognita did
you actually see?
Well she was changing
so I saw her underwear.
You saw Haruhi's underwear?
So what do we do?
There's only one thing to do:
we have to induce amnesia.
Hold him.
That's enough, you two.
Leave assault and battery
to the professionals.
What are you, made of ice? How
can you be so calm about this?
Look! The boss is so deep
in shock he's regressing.
Well, now that it appears
the proverbial cat is
out of the bag. Let's talk.
Haruhi is compelled to hide
the fact that she's a girl
due to certain mitigating
circumstances.
While we can't physically force
you to cooperate exactly,
there is something
I would like for you
to bear in mind.
Coming from the sort of
family you do, I'm certain
you hear all sorts
of juicy little rumors.
Enough to know what
is true and what is not.
Take the Ootori family's
private police force,
the Black Onion Squad.
It is said that
they can be mobilized
against our enemies
in the blink of an eye.
You have heard of them, right?
Clearly this isn't just a talk.
Come on guys. Stop scaring
Casanova. Sorry about all this.
Hey Fujioka.
Look, it's alright.
Doesn't really matter to me.
You can tell
whoever you want to.
Well well, Bossa Nova.
Since you know she's a girl,
are you in love?
Tetsuya, how is the Young Lord?
Did he refuse
to eat dinner again?
Yeah.
Damn it all, what is wrong with
him? Are we not giving him
the moral support
like you told us to?
When is he going to snap
the hell out of this?
And what about kick the can,
huh? Did I chug all those
drinks for nuthin'?
We were supposed to play.
I mean, did you see
his face when he came home
from school today?
The Young Lord looked like
he'd just killed somebody.
Stop it now! Please everyone.
You musn't be discouraged.
The emotional support has
been getting through
to him, I know it.
It's just--
What?
Well it's obvious that
there's something different
weighing on his mind today.
Well then, what's the matter?
As I was bringing the
Young Lord his dinner
earlier this evening--
Young Lord?
Like. Love. Like. Love.
Like. Love.
I knew it! I'm in
love with Fujioka!
So you're saying he's--
In love?
Does the Young Lord
even have a chance?
Oh yeah-- I see the two
of them hanging out together
at school all the time.
Fujioka does have
an unusually cute little
face. I mean, for a guy.
I don't understand.
What does that mean?
Means he's in love with a dude!
I'm sorry about
all this, Casanova.
This is bad.
Now that I know he's
a she I can't get her
out of my mind.
No peeking, you naughty boy.
She's just so cute.
Look, it's alright.
Doesn't matter to me.
You can tell
whoever you want to.
She was-- She was bluffing.
Oh how incredibly brave!
My poor Fujioka!
She must really be
in some kind of
desperate situation
if she has to dress
like a guy and pretend
to be a host!
All right. From this point
forward, I will keep Fujioka's
secret even if
it costs me my life!
It's Kasanoda, from class D.
I heard he made himself
Mori's apprentice.
I wonder if that means he's in
training to be a host, too.
I'd like to request Fujioka.
What is this?
Is he for real?
The genuine article.
At long last!
Renge, is it true?
Is he really--?
Could he really be
that kind of persuasion?
What are they goin'
on about? You know,
before yesterday
people froze in terror
if I so much as looked at them.
But for some reason today
is different. However hard
I glare, no one is freezing.
Just the opposite.
All eyes are on me.
And it burns!
Welcome, Casanova.
So you're our guest today, huh?
Uh, that's right.
Come on, keep it together,
Ritsu. Don't lose your cool.
Would you like to have
some tea? How much sugar
do you normally put in?
Here, uh, let me help.
Now, now. You're
our guest. It's okay.
Tea, made especially for me.
So tell me, is this your first
time in a place like this?
Haha. Gotcha.
You sure have this down, huh?
Well trust me, it didn't
come naturally at all;
at least not at first.
But then I realized
if I just sat back
and had fun with it,
everything sort of fell
into place on its own.
Hey, don't just stand there,
Kyoya-senpai.
Get him out of here.
If he's getting along
with his goons so well now,
why does he need to be here
in the first place?
He has kept Haruhi's secret
so far and, since he is
after all a paying guest, I can
see no reason to eject him.
But the other guests are afraid!
Oh, no I think not.
Observe.
The look on his face
is just priceless.
I've never seen someone
so in love before!
Hello, Sumire? Forget about
you stupid violin lesson
and hightail it to the
Host Club! I'm telling you,
this is a one-in-million
chance to witness
something truly amazing!
Hello, Kurakano? You've got
to get to the Host Club
right now! If you don't,
you'll regret it for
the rest of your life.
See? We're just fine.
Thanks to him we may even set
a new record.
You money-grubbing enabler!
Can I pour you
another cup of tea?
Uh, yes. Thank you.
Oh no, she's giving him
the adorable smile--
--The one which
no man can resist!
Wow. Usually you guys
wouldn't waste any time
interrupting the two of them.
Yeah but our hands are tied.
After our screw-up in
Karuizawa, Haruhi would
never forgive us
if we butted in.
Karuizawa was really
your screw-up, Hikaru.
Hey boss, are you done
being shell-shocked yet?
Yeah, we could really use
our king right about now.
Go get 'em!
Ma.
Tamaki-senpai?
Um, just what exactly
are you doing?
Hey, if you want to sit down,
do it over there.
You can play with this
if you need a distraction.
It's a little freebie I got
at the supermarket when
I bought the instant
coffee earlier.
Look I've solved it, Haruhi.
Wow, that was fast. Okay,
now try to see if you can
put them back together.
Ma.
That moron!
Ma?
Earth to Boss! Will you
snap out of it already?
The longer you sit there like
an idiot playing "robot"
the worse the situation
becomes for all of us!
Ma.
Now, listen to me carefully.
You can't let this happen.
If she and that
two-bit thug hit it off
she's going to spend her life--
as a mob-wife!
Ma?
Lowlife snitch.
You ratted me out!
What? No way!
Daddy won't stand for that!
Ugh. Please don't do this.
Bossa Nova!
Just what do you think
you're trying to do here?
You established a bond
with your henchmen,
didn't you? Why aren't
you with them right now?
You tell him, sir!
Yeah!
What about kick the can?
You remember that?
You should be out there enjoying
life to the fullest with
your friends while you're still
young enough to appreciate
it before it all slips away
right under your nose!
Why are you harassing
my Haruhi?
As her father,
I forbid you to see her.
Wait, what? You're telling me
that you're Fuijoka's dad?
You have got to be kidding me.
That's just not possible.
Oh no.
He's painted the boss
into a corner.
Well, we might not
be related by blood.
Okay, so, what're you
married to her mom then?
No, as a matter of fact.
I've never met the woman.
So I guess you're really
not her father are you?
Wah! Tama-chan!
I'll catch you!
He's right you know.
Strictly speaking,
I'm not Haruhi's real father.
Uh, strictly speaking
or otherwise.
Hey look. He's waking up.
I need to sort this out.
Sort what out exactly?
If supposing I'm not my
Haruhi's daddy after all--
We don't have
to suppose it, Boss.
Then how can it be that I
find her so utterly adorable?
What are you talking about?
When she's with another man,
why is it that I become
so insanely jealous?
I'm not her father. I have no
right to be so protective.
No right whatsoever.
So then, uh, tell me what
exactly is with the whole
"making Haruhi your wife
one day" thing?
I know! Daddy's don't typically
want to marry their
little girls when they're
all grown up do they?
What about keeping her
from kissing anyone?
I only wanted to preserve
those precious lips.
Preserve? Really?
That's a very interesting
choice of words, sir.
You think everything
is absolutely perfect,
just the way it is now.
And having this family
setting will keep it all
from changing, right?
Hey Kaoru?
I don't understand.
He's an idiot!
Is he really that oblivious?
Actually, he's got a point.
I mean, you're delusional,
yes, any halfwit could
see that but who knew
that you were so--?
Tama-chan's completely blind
when it comes to himself!
Kaoru, just what did you mean
by things changing?
Oh.
Nothing. Just a little
theory I have.
Which I'm probably
completely wrong about.
You think everything's
alright over there? I mean,
I didn't say anything
to set him off, did I?
Who knows? Although,
when I think about it,
Tamaki-senpai is like
my dad in some ways.
Did you hear that gentlemen?
Apparently in some ways
I am like Haruhi's father!
Well to be more precise,
I think what she's saying is
that while you and
her father do share some
personality traits,
in actuality-
I've got it! I've got it now!
I'm like a father to her!
And we've lost him yet again.
Fujioka. Um.
Do you think that we could
maybe do this more often?
Because, I was just thinking,
since you entertain girls
all day long it might kind of
give you a break from all that.
You know, if I came around.
I mean if--if you
want that, that is.
Absolutely! That way you and
I could get more aquainted.
Here it comes!
Fujioka, I--
Loosing control.
Can't hold back feelings--
I, uh, have something to say.
I just wanted to tell you.
I just wanted
to tell you. That I'm--
That you're excited to have
someone you can relate to,
aren't you?
I know I sure am.
A conversation like this is
a rare thing for me.
We're going to be
great friends.
Uh oh. Hung out to dry.
He totally just got shot down!
He didn't even get a chance
to profess his love!
Oh. The friends thing.
That really stings!
I bet that rejection haunts
him for the rest of his life.
Aw, the poor guy.
It's so tragic.
Okay. Did not think
that one through.
I guess if she has
to live her life as a guy,
dating a guy would probably
raise some suspicions.
So be it, then. For Fujioka's
sake, there's only
one thing to do.
Of course the two of us
are going to be friends!
Best of friends! Forever!
Bossa Nova!
Kasanoda!
Casanova!
How lovely.
How absolutely beautiful!
You've moved us to tears!
We'll be your friends!
That was breathtaking!
Do it again!
We want to be friends
with you, too, Boss Nova!
Let's play kick the can!
I know I'm your senpai,
but I'll still be your friend!
You can even hold Usa-chan!
I'll include a
special piece on you in
"Moe Moe Ouran Diaries,
Vol. 11!"
Adieu, brave one!
What's the matter, Tamaki?
When I think about
how Bossa Nova must have
been feeling, my heart
goes out to him a little.
That's strange, isn't it?
I mean, as Haruhi's father,
you shouldn't feel
sympathy for the man
who tried to take your
precious little girl away,
now should you?
Hyper Starlight Kick!
One. Two. Three. Four.
Here quick! In here!
Hey, what are you doing?
This hiding place is only
for Haruhi and me, got it?
What kind of a rule is that?
Yeah! And for that matter,
why do you and Haruhi
always have to hide together
in the first place?
Idiot! It is perfectly natural
for a father to hide
with his daughter!
Some might disagree.
Would all of you just be quiet!
So, Hika-chan may seem
oblivious, but deep down
he's beginning to
understand his feelings?
And even though it's clear
to the rest of us
how Tama-chan feels,
he's still completely
in the dark about it himself?
Yeah.
Then what about
Kao-chan and Kyo-chan?
Between the two of them, I'll
bet there's someone even more
oblivious than Tama-chan is.
Considering that, I wonder
if something really big
is gonna happen
before we graduate.
You never know.
Well for starters,
why even kick the can?
Hey, stop pushing so hard.
Get your hands off my Haruhi!
She doesn't belong to you!
Oh yeah! If not me, then who?
I do not belong to anybody!
Kyoya-senpai, how does someone
cool like you get roped
into something as crazy
as the Host Club?
The secret of the Host Club's
birth is about to be revealed!
Will you please shut up?
Next time:
"And so Kyoya Met Him."
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you.
We'll see you then.