Oh, there you are Shiro. The
rest of the club is assembled
and ready to go. You should
get to the music room.
I'm sorry sir, but I'm quitting
the Classical Music Club.
Huh? What made you decide
to quit all of a sudden?
I think you have a natural
talent for the piano- it'd be
a shame to waste it. So forget
about quitting and come back
to the club.
If you play piano,
you're sure to be popular
with all the ladies.
But that's gonna take too long!
I don't have that much time!
The top floor
of the south building,
at the end
of the north hallway.
In a music room
that's never used.
This is it. This is the place.
Welcome to the Ouran Host Club.
Oh, it's just a kid.
Not only that, it's just a boy.
What's wrong, little boy?
Did you come to my palace
in search of something?
Um, are you the king
of this place?
Well, are you?
Come closer, lost one.
What was it that you
just called me, little boy?
The "King"?
The "King"! Yes, I'm the king
of the Ouran host club!
Long live the host king!
I'm an elementary
5th year, Shiro Takaoji!
I want the Host Club King to
take me on as an apprentice!
The Grade-School Host
is the Naughty Type!
Oh my, Tamaki,
you have an apprentice?
Yes. He's still
in elementary school,
but I like
the fire in his eyes.
But are you sure it's okay
for such a young boy
to become a host?
Why wouldn't it be? Love
has nothing to do with age.
Take us, For instance,
whenever I look at you,
my heart starts pounding.
Suddenly, I feel no different
than a lovesick little boy.
Oh, Tamaki.
Don't you think it's weird
that he's making the kid
observe him
up close like that?
There is a theory
that people are considered
more beautiful the closer they
are viewed. Tamaki seems to
live by that theory.
Well, let's leave them alone.
You naughty girl,
you've drawn me
to the forbidden fruit, dearest.
You're a mermaid who's
brought light into my lonely
sea. My mermaid princess.
I remind you of a mermaid?
You look more like the carp
that swim in my pond at home.
I'd never give false
compliments like that!
Carp?
Oh, don't listen to him.
He's just a kid-
you know how kids are-
they can't help but be honest.
Honest?
But that's just his opinion!
I wouldn't say that
you look like a carp. And even
if you did look like a carp,
you'd be the most beautiful
carp of them all!
So I am a carp!
Uh, no, that's
not what I meant.
Tamaki, you're an idiot!
No wait! Mermaid Princess!
Man, what a crybaby.
So how's it going, boss?!
That's an adorable little
apprentice you've got there.
Hikaru, do you wish you had
a little brother like Shiro?
Don't be silly. I could search
the globe and I'd never find
a better brother
than you, Kaoru.
Hikaru.
Look! They're doing it!
It's forbidden brotherly love!
They're homos!
And they're brothers!
That makes this totally
"insectuous"!
I think what you meant to say
was incestuous.
Hey Shiro-chan!
You wanna have
a piece of cake with me?
We've got three kinds:
chocolate, strawberry and lime.
Hey, back off! What grade
are you in, anyway?!
Why are you wearing
a high school uniform?
Something wrong, Mitsukuni?
That's not fair! A little kid
like you isn't supposed
to have a cool,
older friend like him!
Are you alright?
I know. It's kinda hard
to get used to all
the weirdos around here. It took
me a while to get adjusted
to all the craziness,
so don't freak out.
I'm sure you'll get used to it.
This one kinda acts
like a girl.
Something wrong?
Are you a cross-dresser?
Oh, no.
Okay, that's enough.
I think Shiro should take care
of the tea for us,
don't you?
Wow, Haruhi, you're
looking extra manly today!
Now do what the boss says
and let Shiro take care
of that tea set,
it's part of his training.
You're too macho
for tea sets.
This kid is smarter
than I thought.
He may be a kid
but he's got quite an eye.
Now be careful with it.
It's pretty heavy.
It's not my fault
I dropped it.
It's your fault 'cause
you're the one who made me
take it in the first place.
Say what?
Haruhi, that's
another 100,000 yen.
Hey! You should
make the cross-dresser do
all your stupid chores!
I'm not here to carry
tea sets- I'm here to learn
how to make women happy!
You won't get anywhere
with that attitude.
And I am not going to let you
disrespect Haruhi. So!
Put this brat in isolation!
You got it, boss!
What's going on here?!
Why'd you put me in
a cage all of a sudden?!
Yeah, where'd it come from?
This is supposed to be
a music room, right?
This is no way to treat
your loyal apprentice!
Now let me out of this cage!
Not until you've learned
your lesson. I made you
my apprentice because I thought
you were serious about
becoming a host but
I guess I was wrong.
I am serious.
Totally serious.
I want you to teach me
how to make a woman happy!
I'm gonna run out of time.
Please, won't you teach me?
You're a host because
you like girls.
You like bringing a smile
to a girl's face- that's why
you do it, right?
Please, won't you teach me
how to be like you?
You're a genius at it!
You're the king!
Well, you may be a brat,
but I admire your desire
to become a host,
so I'll teach you.
You know, Shiro,
you and I are so much alike.
You poor kid.
Then you'll help me
become the kind of host
that can make any woman happy?!
Of course, making women
happy is the sole purpose
of being a host. If this is
what you really want Shiro,
then you have to figure out
how to use the material
you already have.
What does that mean?
You see, here at
the Ouran Host Club.
Our policy is to use our
individual personality traits
to meet the needs
of our guests. For example,
there's Tamaki, who is
the princely type.
There's the strong,
silent type.
The boy Lolita type.
The little devil type.
And the cool type.
It's all about variety.
And now our group is complete
with the addition
of Haruhi, the natural.
The natural?
It would seem that right now
we have a perfect blend
of characteristics,
so it's going to be
difficult to find
a new type for Shiro.
If you go by his age, he
should be the boy Lolita type.
But Honey-senpai's
already got that covered.
Is he gonna replace me?
Oh come on! Is that
all you've got?
What's up with this place? It's
supposed to be a music room.
Sorry to interrupt gentlemen,
but what's with the lackluster
character analysis? I must
say, I'm quite disappointed.
I thought I taught you better.
Alright then, Miss Manager.
How would you work Shiro
into our collection of
characters? He can't be
the boy Lolita because Honey's
already got that covered.
You just don't
get it, do you?
Now listen up! There are
plenty of girls out there
who have a thing for younger
boys or boys with baby faces.
These girls would be
considered shota fans.
Now, shota can be
a fairly broad category
so it's important to know
that the genre can be
broken down into many different
smaller sub-categories.
For example, shota fans with
an interest in Lolita boys
would favor a boy like
Haninozuka-senpai.
But this little boy is
different. If I had to pick
a character for him.
Yes! He'd be the naughty-boy
type, without a doubt!
The naughty type?
Now to play up
the naughty type,
you have to wear shorts, okay!
You've gotta have
bumps and bruises!
Give him a couple of scars!
Run like a spoiled child!
Make it reckless!
Now I want you to trip
and make it big!
"Are you okay, little boy?"
Now give them
your catch phrase!
No big deal,
it was nothin'.
That was perfect!
Absolutely perfect, Shiro!
That was outstanding.
I never knew you were such
a great coach, Renge.
They're idiots!
They're all a bunch of idiots!
I've had enough of you people!
This is so stupid- none
of this is ever gonna help me
make her happy!
Who's her?
Wait Shiro! We haven't
taught you how
to apply the techniques
you've learned yet!
I swear, younger boys
are good for nothing.
I went to all that trouble
to coach him, and he quits.
I can't believe
he ditched us because
he didn't like the lesson.
What a selfish little brat.
There aren't many people who'd
enjoy that kinda lesson.
But never mind that, were you
listening to what he said?
I'm gonna run out of time.
Please, won't you teach me?
He said he was "gonna run out
of time"- what do you think
that means? I think,
maybe, it's a girl.
How did we let them
talk us into this?
It'll be okay, Haru-chan.
It was so easy to sneak in
and wearing this uniform
I really look like
I'm in elementary school.
Yeah, you do. I understand
why they wanted you
to wear an elementary
school uniform.
I mean, we are sneaking
into an elementary school
and you totally fit in,
senpai. What I don't understand
is why they made me dress up
in this middle school uniform.
Alright men, it's time
to initiate our mission.
What do you mean?
What mission?
I've assessed the situation.
We'll infiltrate
the elementary school.
You two are going in!
But where are we going?
Why did we even bother
with disguises?
We stick out like a sore thumb!
Oh, there's a reason,
a damn good reason.
This way, Haru-chan!
Isn't she the cutest?
Look at her in that miniskirt.
Haruhi looks like a little doll.
So basically, you just wanted to
see her dressed up like that.
This is it.
Shiro-chan's classroom.
When I was in elementary school
this was my classroom, too!
There's nobody here.
So the kid's classroom
is empty, is it?
This sure takes me back.
I wonder if doodles
are still on my desk.
Doubtful, the school changes
out the desks every year.
Let's check out
the cafeteria after this.
I wanna see the old gym.
Good idea, Kaoru!
Hey! If you're gonna
barge in here like that
then why'd we have to sneak in
here in these stupid disguises?
Don't worry about it.
There's no one here
to catch us.
If the teacher finds us-
-we'll have a hard time
explaining why we snuck in.
Shut up you guys!
Keep your lips
zipped, got it?
Haruhi's the cutest
thing I've ever seen!
It's alright, he's gone.
But you guys, we came here
to get the scoop on Shiro,
so what do you think
we should do now?
Well, Here's
something interesting.
What'd you find?
Hey! That's Shiro!
So he's in the
Classical Music Club.
He looks like
he's enjoying himself.
It's nice to see him with
a smile on his face.
I had no idea he
could look so sweet.
Yeah.
There he is!
There's Shiro-chan!
Excuse me, Takaoji?
I'm sorry, but have you been
practicing the new piece
teacher gave us?
The new piece? Not really.
If you want I can show it
to you. Do you wanna
come play it with me?
No thanks, you go ahead.
After all, there's
only one grand piano.
You should use it, Kahmishiro.
Thank you! I will then!
And if you want to join me
just let me know.
Pardon me, mademoiselle.
I've never seen a rose more
lovely than you, my dear.
Here, this is for you.
I was wondering if you could
tell me anything about
that young lady playing
the piano. Do you know her?
That's Hina Kameeshido.
Her name is Hina?
That's right, But you better
not fall in love with her.
Why?
Didn't you know? Hina
has to move away soon.
Her dad just got a new job
in Germany, so they have to
move there at
the end of the week.
What do you
think you're doing?!
I want you idiots
to leave immediately!
Put me down!
What are you doing?!
Let me go! Just put me down!
Where do you think...
It's time to go, guys.
Quit thrashing around.
What is your problem,
you big idiot?!
I'm sorry but
you're the idiot.
You said that you wanted
me to teach you how
to make women happy.
But that's not it, is it?
You're not concerned with the
happinesss of just any woman.
You've got your sights set on
one woman in particular.
You only care about one,
and that's Hina Kamishiro.
But I'm afraid there's
nothing I can do
to help you with that, Shiro.
Listen, Shiro.
I know that I told you,
it's the job of a host
to make women happy.
But when you care
for someone, you must
find the courage to express
what is in your heart.
You have to tell her
how you feel about her.
You didn't come to me looking
to become a full-fledged host.
You want to be
a full-fledged man.
It doesn't matter anymore.
I've run out of time.
I just I wanted to hear her
play before she left for good.
That's all.
That piece she played.
It's Mozart's Sonata in D major
for 2 Pianos, isn't it?
Wait a minute, since when
is there a grand piano
in this room?
Well, this is a music
room, after all.
So why wouldn't it
have a grand piano?
It is a music room, after all.
It is a music room.
It's always been there.
We just had it covered up.
Awesome.
Hey Takaoji. I noticed
that you're always
listening to me when I'm
playing. Do you like the piano?
If so then why don't
we learn to play together?
She played beautifully, but it
wasn't the piano that I liked.
For the next week you
will spend your mornings,
lunches, recesses,
and free-time after school
in piano lessons with me.
But, why?
You wanted to be
my apprentice, right?
Besides, that young lady
looked like she wanted
nothing more than
to play piano with you.
Welcome, princess,
we've been waiting.
I present to you, Shiro
Takaoji's piano recital.
If you please, princess.
Let's play together, Hina.
Okay!
We did a good thing.
He loves with all his heart.
So I guess that's
one more way Shiro
takes after you, huh, senpai?
Why, yes, I'd say so.
So you've been exchanging
emails with Hina everyday
now that she's in Germany?
Yeah, more or less.
I like her but she can get
pretty jealous for
an elementary school girl.
She'd be upset if she knew
I was with you ladies,
so let's keep this
our little secret.
Oh! Isn't he the cutest?!
His little girlfriend
is so lucky!
I wish I had a little
brother just like him!
Naughty boys are the best!
I could kiss you.
You brat, what are you doing.
Those are my guests.
Well, it looks like they've
found someone they like better.
It was so easy
to steal your customers.
I think there's
a new host king in town.
I thought he'd make it through
without exploding this time.
We should've known he was
gonna blow up sooner or later.
Shiro really does have a lot
in common with Tamaki-senpai.
I get the feeling that senpai
was also a spoiled brat
when he was a kid.
I was not a spoiled brat!
I was nothing like him
when I was a kid!
I was a sweet, innocent,
precocious, adorable child!
You hear me?!
All right,
we're headed to the pool!
We'll finally get to see
Haruhi in a swimsuit!
Oh, no! Honey-senpai is being
pulled away by the current!
Next time,
"Jungle Pool SOS"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!