Since adopting the zaibatsu
system as its corporate model
generations ago, the Otori
Group has advanced
the medical field to
unprecedented heights.
Today, we continue that
proud history of innovation
and leadership through
our cutting-edge approach
to hospital administration.
A prospective successor
to this legacy will do well
to remember that merely
standing in the shadow
of his brothers' achievements
will not suffice
to ensure his future.
Hey, Kyoya, I just had
the most brilliant idea!
How did I wind up here?
Mama, hurry up!
It's right over here!
Alright, alright.
I was sleeping comfortably
in my own bed just
a few minutes ago. No, wait.
Tamaki was carrying on
about some sort of exhibit.
He had his heart set on all
of us going, I think.
Doesn't this sound fascinating?
Commoners hold events
like these all the time.
They're called "expos,"-
That's commoner lingo
for "exposition."
Products from all over are
gathered under one roof
so that underprivileged
people can cope with
the emptiness of
not being able to travel.
That makes this the
perfect opportunity for us
to better understand Haruhi,
by allowing the Host Club
to study commoners in
their natural environment.
You guessed it, Kyoya. We're
going to go on a field trip!
Haruhi won't
be joining us today,
incidentally as her
presence might harm our
credibility as
impartial observers.
Oh, come on. You can't just
lie here in bed all morning!
Today's the last day
of summer vacation!
For your information I was
up until 5am, you morons.
Which if you hadn't
noticed makes me
a little less than happy
about being woken up.
Kyo-chan isn't much
a morning person, huh?
You have no room to talk.
Hey what does that mean?
Okay Enough with
the commoner shtick.
If you formulaic halfwits feel
like wasting all afternoon
on worn-out old clichés.
Go right ahead
and suit yourselves.
Well, if that's
what you really want.
You heard the man. Now let's
dress him to the nines
and head for the Expo!
Hey Everyone! Look at that!
Wow, all of those suits
look exactly the same!
Mass production!
They have something here called
a pet shop! That will be
our very first
destination, men!
They serve ice cream
on the roof-top!
They're holding some
super-special event
up there, too! Sweet!
What kind of event?
Ice cream!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Oh right. That's how.
Looks like I'm at the Izumi
shopping center, which isn't
exactly within in walking
distance of home.
Guess I'll call
to have a car sent out.
Yay!
Oh, wow, sorry.
Mama!
Tamaki's a dead man
when I get my hands on him.
Kyoya-senpai?
I didn't expect
to see you here today.
How much money do you
have on you, Haruhi?
What?
Kyoya's Reluctant Day Out.
Kyoya-senpai. Are you sure
this is where you want to eat?
There are much
nicer restaurants
to choose from upstairs.
Well, you don't
have much on you,
so our choices are limited.
Just be sure to get a receipt.
Tamaki will
reimburse you tenfold.
How did this happen? All
I wanted was a little peek
at the products expo.
Why did I have to run
into Kyoya-senpai?
And why did he have
to be in such a foul mood?
Haruhi, I think it's
our turn. How do I order?
Oh, uh here. Why don't
I order for both of us?
Do you know what you want?
You pick. Just get us
a lot of it.
Well, Okay. That and that one.
Both with fries too please.
He's so cute,
and just my type!
Okay Coming right up.
Would you be interested
in adding one of our
delicious dessert.
Thank you, no.
I don't care for sweets.
Gorgeous and cool,
I think I'm in love!
Before you decide, we have
a new shake that's absolutely-
I have given you my answer.
Please be sure
to include our receipt.
Kyoya-senpai.
Just because you're in a bad
mood today doesn't give you
the right to go around
talking to people that way.
The poor girl was
just doing her job.
Her job is to serve us food,
not irritate me with some
weak sales pitch.
Now what?
Nothing, I just don't think
I've ever actually seen you
eat before. Somehow I thought
the experience would be
more refined. I'm surprised
this food even appeals to you.
It doesn't appeal to me
in the slightest.
No doubt you'll say I'm
callous for admitting it,
since you bought this tripe.
Of course not.
I will think it, though.
There is an understanding
between makers of food like
this and those that eat it
- quality takes a backseat
to convenience.
Refinement isn't part
of the equation.
It's meant to be eaten quickly.
Besides, no one of consequence
is here to witness my
momentary lapse of manners.
He must be taking a break from
the whole "nice guy" act today.
I guess rich people have
to let their hair down every
once in a while.
Hey.
For the record I'm saying
that it benefits me nothing
to keep up appearances
in a place like this.
And that includes
any special treatment
I might give you here.
Really? Never would
have guessed that
in a million years.
Oh my gosh, girls!
That guy in the glasses
is a total hottie.
You're right. He's gorgeous!
Excuse me.
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
I was wondering
if you're not using this chair
can my friends
and I borrow it?
Why not?
Thank you so much!
That's awesome!
You're quite welcome.
I've never seen
this side of Kyoya before.
Is he always this indifferent
when there's nothing
for him to gain?
Welcome. Won't you come in?
Tamaki couldn't be this
apathetic if his life
depended on it. How is it
that the two of them
compliment each other so well?
You're probably wondering
how Tamaki and I
compliment each other so well.
Oh great -now he's
inside my head!
What is he, psychic?!
The answer is simple.
I have something to gain.
There's no better motivator
than self-interest.
I have to look out for
number one, you know.
Tamaki-senpai would be crushed
if he heard you say that.
On the contrary.
He's understood our arrangement
from the very beginning.
The same goes for all
of them: Hikaru, Kaoru,
Honey-senpai, Mori-senpai.
The glue that holds the
Host Club together is
our mutual egocentricity.
It's the principle that
drives the alliance between
our families and ensures
each of our futures. Though.
Well, let's just say
there's still quite a bit
you don't understand
about that.
Although Tamaki's a fool and
self-sacrifice does come
naturally to him.
So I guess the point of this
is we are very
different creatures.
Senpai, I thought you were
going to take a taxi home.
I am, but I might as well
have a look around first.
Black pearls from
Ishigaki Island.
Odd to find them here,
considering how much
they go for.
You're kidding. Really?
That's incredible.
How can you tell, senpai?
I am the product
of excellent breeding.
Breeding, huh?
Well, That would account
for the wall of ice
he's putting up between us.
So, Kyoya-senpai, why is it
that after all this time
I still know next to
nothing about your family?
Because there's really
nothing for you to know
about my family, at least
nothing that should
be of interest to you.
Well that seems a little bit
unfair, don't you think?
Just what do you mean "unfair?"
I mean that when it comes
to my personal life,
you even keep tabs
on who my father's friends
from work are while I barely
have a clue about yours-
So I call that unfair.
That's a very intriguing
notion, in its own way.
You've got two older
brothers, right?
For starters, you could tell
me something about them.
What kind of people are they?
Please allow me
to introduce my sons.
They are the Otori legacy.
Ah. What fine
young men they are.
Truly a credit to their line.
You must be very pleased.
They all appear to be
remarkably brilliant,
though of course only the
oldest will succeed his father.
Kyoya is the most
handsome of the three,
but you're right -
with two older brothers
ahead of him
he doesn't stand a chance
of becoming the
family's patriarch.
They're rather exceptional.
Enough so that my father
puts a lot of stock in them.
Though as the third son,
things work out
a little differently for me.
An irreproachable academic
record and social finesse
are accomplishments your
brothers laid claim
to long ago, so your own
achievements will have to
outshine these considerably in
order to impress me, Kyoya.
I didn't realize there
was so much pressure
on you to succeed.
Pressure?
Oh no, Haruhi.
I can think of nothing
more fun than this.
Dear me, pieces from the
Komatsu Shoin collection.
I never thought that
I would find them here.
Why Madam, you have
an astonishing eye.
Um, Senpai?
You know, they have such
exquisite color, don't they?
To tell you the truth,
I'm not really even
supposed to have
these out on display.
The bulk of the Komatsu
collection has been
privately held for ages.
Pieces rarely come up for sale.
With all due respect,
these are fake.
Hey, get out of here, kid.
What do you think you're doing?
The shade of blue
is strongly reminiscent
of Shoin's work,
but looking closely
around the base you'll
notice the color graduation
isn't quite dark
enough to be authentic -
that and the lacquer
is too clear.
That's enough out
of you, Mr. Expert!
I'll report you for
obstructing my business!
Just as I thought.
The brushstrokes on this seal
are uncharacteristically broad
as well.
For your sake I hope
you have a certificate.
That is if you
still insist it's real.
Of course it's real! I have
the certificate at home!
Ah, then surely
you won't mind if I call
the Komatsu family right now
to verify your claim.
My own family has
had dealings with them
for generations.
It would only be
a matter of minutes.
Young man,
I can't thank you enough.
After everything
you've told me, Senpai,
stepping in on
a complete stranger's behalf
seems a little out
of character for you.
Oh, that? Well, now,
she's hardly a stranger.
You mean you don't know?
Her husband is the CEO of a
major electronics company.
Allow me to--
This is my first time
to meet her personally.
But the ring on her
left hand is unmistakable.
My family has dealings
with her husband's company.
Ah, one of the Ootori boys!
Imagine running
into you here incognito!
The next opportunity
I have, I'll be sure
to take advantage
of one of your family's
beautiful health resorts.
We'd be honored.
Big surprise. Kyoya-senapi
is Kyoya-senpai after all.
Now hang on a second-
That woman's ring.
There's no way
he could have.
Hey, Haruhi.
Did you know this?
Did I know what?
Is melon the preferred
flavor among snack makers?
It doesn't make sense.
If the primary ingredient
is corn, why go to the trouble
of artificially making
it taste like fruit?
Seems counter-intuitive.
That's an intriguing notion,
in its own way.
Oh, was I being funny?
Earlier you were
going on and on about how
you and Tamaki-senpai
are nothing alike,
but what you just
said about the candy?
It sounds exactly like him!
You think so?
This does seem like
something he and the twins
would fawn over.
Very well, I'll buy them.
Haruhi, your wallet.
Oh yeah, I forgot. Just be
sure to save me your receipt.
No, you're too heavy!
Oh! You're too heavy!
Hey Tama-chan,
the show's about to start!
Hey, kiddos,
I hope you're ready!
It's back to school time!
Have all of you
boys and girls
been keeping up with your
summer homework assignments?
What's that?
Ugh! You haven't!
What have you been
doing all this time?
Stop goofing around
and get a move on!
What is Renge doing up there?
It seems like recently-
-she's practically
been around every corner.
What do we have here?
A bunch of naughty
little children
who aren't ready for school?
It's too late now!
I, Doctor Namahage,
will never let you leave!
This is a job for
The Ouran Host Club Rangers!
Unhand her!
Oh no! It's my arch nemesis,
dreaded shadow leader
of the Host Rangers!
Host Black!
Um, what happened
to Kyo-chan??
Uh.
Hey, senpai?
Why do you think
Tamaki-senpai is always
so eager
to help people in need?
You mean when
there's nothing to be gained
from it? Who knows?
So then, when you help
someone, how exactly do you
benefit from it?
Money, or fame?
A specific material gain
of some sort?
Or is it more abstract?
Because as I see it,
Tamaki gets something out of
helping others that doesn't
necessarily involve
their paying him back.
So maybe when you get right
down to it -the two of you
aren't that all different.
Kyoya.
Would you find a map of all the
public schools in this area?
I'd like to help this man
find his daughter.
Besides, that young lady looked
like she wanted nothing more
than to play piano with you
It's an absolute tragedy
to see a brother and sister
at odds this way!
We have to do something
to help them!
If you really want to
surpass your brothers,
then you can do it,
but I think you're the one
who's lost hope
and given up.
Hey, Kyoya, I just had
the most brilliant idea!
We should start
a club together.
Attention shoppers. This is an
announcement for a lost child.
A little boy named Kyoya Otori
is lost inside the store.
Repeat: Kyoya Otori is lost.
His guardian Suou
is waiting for him at the
2nd floor information counter.
Kyoya is 5-feet, 11-inches
tall, with black hair
and wearing
prescription glasses.
Is that him?
Matches the description.
He's a little big to be lost,
don't you think?
Hey mister, is there
something wrong with you?
That damn idiot.
I'll kill him!
Oh Kyoya!
There you are!
We were so worried
-why is Haruhi with you?
Oh boy! Oh boy! Haru-chan
has come to play with us!
Hooray! Play! Play!
Play! Play!
I'm sorry, guys,
but I'm exhausted.
It has been
a very long day for me.
Hey, stop it! Quit licking me!
That tickles!
What's with the dog?
Isn't she beautiful?
I got her at this amazing
place they call a pet shop.
Hey! Cut it out, Antoinette!
How exactly am I
like this moron?
I know you want me to
believe your only reasons
for helping that woman
earlier were selfish ones.
But that isn't
the truth, is it?
Because from where
we were standing.
There's no way you could
have seen her ring.
There was a flag
blocking our view.
It just doesn't make sense.
You go to all that trouble
acting like you're such
a big jerk when being a nice
guy comes so naturally to you-
-it seems counter-intuitive.
That's a very intriguing
notion, in its own way.
Hey, what's going on?!
Who is that kid?
Oh, this ought to be good!
You'll have to do better
than that, Chika-chan!
Next time, "Chika's 'Down
with Honey' Declaration."
The Ouran Host Club will
be waiting for you.
We'll see you then.