Only those with excellent
social standing and those
from filthy rich families
are lucky enough to spend
their time here at the elite,
private school, Ouran Academy.
The Ouran Host Club is where
the school's handsomest boys,
with too much time on their
hands, entertain young ladies
who also have way too much
time on their hands.
Just think of it as Ouran
Academy's elegant playground
for the super-rich
and beautiful.
Welcome, ladies!
So, in which cup would my
princess like her tea?
The Foley? The Worcester?
Or perhaps
the Susie Cooper Gardenia?
Beautiful.
These are English antiques,
aren't they?
Which one do
you like, Tamaki?
Which one?
Well, none of these
compare to my princess.
Oh wow.
I don't really know
what to say.
You mean, you've never been
to Covent Garden?
No, all of our antiques
are from Portobello Road.
I think you'd like
Covent Garden.
Most of our Victorian
pieces are from there.
Kaoru!
Honestly Kaoru,
you have to be more careful.
From now on keep
your eyes on me, okay?
Yes, Hikaru.
I can't take it!
It's overwhelming!
You have to watch this!
You may not
get another chance!
Who knows when
it'll happen again!
You are absolutely right,
mademoiselle.
All beauty is fleeting,
just take a look
at these cherry blossoms.
You'll never be able
to see them this vibrant again.
And that's why I've compiled
this picture book that contains
photos that capture the
beauty of each passing day.
Incidentally, I've prepared
similar books of the other hosts
as well. And if you ladies
are interested in collecting
all four of them, I'll
discount the full set for you.
I'll take them!
Me too, please!
Well, now we know how
the club makes extra money.
But I have to wonder.
When did he
take pictures of us?
Should I say
something to him?
Mitsukuni.
You overdid it.
He told him!
Honey, I'll take it!
It looks so yummy!
It's just the right
amount for both of us!
Any more would be too much!
How'd did you know?
You never cease to amaze me!
Really?
Haruhi, how are you doing?
Are you having a good time?
Tamaki-senpai.
The flower-viewing reception
is going over quite well.
But even so, it's rather
daunting to spend more time
being admired than
doing the admiring.
Oh wow Senpai, you're blooming
in more ways than one?
You noticed!
Yes, today my beauty
is quite splendorous!
I'm in full bloom! I bet
you'll fall for me soon.
I swear this guy must live
his life completely unaware
of the hardships
of this world.
So, Haruhi, have you decided
your elective courses
for this term?
How about
Conversational French?
I don't know.
I think the three of us
should take it together.
It makes perfect sense.
We are in the same class.
Say, Mommy, dear?
What is it now, Daddy?
I have a new theory.
I mean, it's just my
hypothesis but it seems that
by being in the same class,
Hikaru and Kaoru
are able to spend more time
with Haruhi than I get to
here at the club. This
gives them a chance to get
close to her.
And if that happens--
Tamaki, you just now
realized that?
According to my research,
in a single day,
the twins spend roughly nine
hours of class time with Haruhi.
Meanwhile, your contact
with her is limited to
a couple of hours of club
activities. In other words,
your involvement in
Haruhi's life each day amounts
to no more than a mere
3 percent. I'm so very sorry.
I don't want to hear it!
Listen Haruhi, I want you to
stop hanging out with those
shady twins from now on!
Who're you calling shady?
Yeah, take a good look
at yourself, boss!
Yes, that's it.
Alright then, we can't go on
hiding the fact that
you're a girl from everyone
in the school any longer!
All Daddy wants is for you to
go back to being the girl you
used to be! For you to surround
yourself with girl friends
and start leading
a wholesome life!
Who're you calling "Daddy"?
So do it! Change back,
now! Change, right now!
You don't have to rush things.
She's going to be
found out soon enough.
Physical exams are
the day after tomorrow.
Physical exams?
That's right,
I forgot all about it.
Then that means, there's
no doubt, they're gonna know
I'm really a girl.
Beware the Physical Exam!
Haruhi!
Been waiting long?
What's the matter?
You look a little down.
I can't help it, everyone keeps
staring at me for some reason.
I'm so embarrassed.
They're looking at you
because you are lovely.
Don't you worry, I promise
that I will protect you
no matter what.
Oh, Senpai, that
makes me feel better.
Thank you, I mean it.
I'm in love-love with you,
Tamaki-senpai!
Oh, you!--
He must be having
a great day dream!
He's kind of creeping me out.
Envious, Hikaru? This is
all part of my strategy.
While you've wasted time
blinded by your jealousy
I've foreseen
the outcome of this charade.
This anime is obviously
a romantic school comedy.
Haruhi and I are the main
characters so that means
we are love interests.
Yeah, then what are we?
You boys are the homosexual
supporting cast!
So, please make sure that you
don't step across this line?
You've got to be kidding.
Hey, listen boss.
I don't think you get it.
If word gets out that
Haru-chan is really a girl
then she won't be able to
be in the Host Club anymore.
But if Haru-chan started
wearing girls' clothes,
I bet she'd be even
cuter than she is now!
She dressed like
a regular girl when she was
in middle school, right? She
must have been pretty popular
with all the boys.
Yeah. According to my
investigative report,
someone would declare their
undying love to her at least
once a month.
Oh, I see. So the boss
wouldn't even be able
to get close to her.
But we'd be able to because
we're in class with her
all day long.
No way!
Hey guys, sorry I'm so late.
Don't you worry, Haruhi! We're
determined to keep your secret.
No one will find out that
you're really a girl during
tomorrow's physical exams!
So please, promise you'll stay
our beloved secret princess!
Sure.
You know what, I think
both of us would be
a little peeved if we had
to watch all the guys
flirt with her.
Then that settles it.
Listen up, squad members.
At tomorrow's physical
exams, position yourselves
in Formation A and then
wait for your orders.
Yes, sir!
I've got it. You guys are
worried cause if they find out
I'm a girl I can't be a host and
therefore can't repay my debt.
My balance is 5,333,332 yen.
Well guess I'll have
to come up with another way
to pay you back.
Do something! The subject
doesn't appear to have
any motivation!
Why'd we get stuck with
such a difficult heroine?
Are you saying that
you hate being a host?
That you hate this club?
Well, to be honest,
I'd have to say yes.
I mean, you guys
aren't bad but if it gets out
I'm a girl there's
nothing I can do, you know?
She doesn't seem to care
one way or the other.
Well before we do anything else
we have to find a way
to motivate her.
Fancy tuna.
Oh, that's right. You didn't
get the chance to eat any
during last episode's
party, did you?
Did you hear that?
She's never eaten fancy tuna
before. Isn't that awful?
Wow, talk about
a difficult childhood.
If only Haru-chan could
stay in the host club,
she'd have the chance to eat
all kinds of yummy things
whenever she wants.
What are you talking about?
Don't be silly!
Just cause I'm poor and
I've never had it doesn't mean
that I'm so much of a glutton
I'd go on fooling everyone
about my gender just
to try some fancy tuna.
Am I really gonna
get to try it?
We will begin conducting
physical examinations shortly.
All students, please proceed
to the clinic in your respective
school building.
So what's the deal with
is this "Formation A" thing
you guys were talking about?
What do they do during
physical exams here
at Ouran anyway?
It's no different than
a physical exam you'd get
at any other school.
Yeah, why would a physical
exam be any different
for us just because we're rich?
You're right. I didn't think
about it that way.
Welcome, students.
But what, what is all this?
Just another physical exam.
The usual.
The usual?
Excuse me, Hitachiin Brothers.
Please follow me this way
to have your height measured.
Sure thing.
Mr. Fujioka?
I'm your nurse for the
physical exams this afternoon.
Okay.
Please, come this way.
Why are Honey and Mori
dressed as doctors?
I don't know--
Honey-senpai!
Mori-senpai!
You're so obvious.
I've got those two
for back up just in case
something happens.
But why are they
in doctor disguises?
They're just helping
to set the mood.
Disguises make our
operation feel like
a real espionage mission.
Wow, Miss Shiramine,
you've lost two whole
kilograms since this time
last year.
That's so good to hear!
I thought for sure
I was heavier!
Not at all! Keep it up
and you'll be even healthier
next year. Good work!
Don't you think it's weird
that these doctors are
all so jovial and nice?
They're chosen by
the school's chairman.
This may be a school
but it's also a business.
Therefore he wants
to keep the students happy.
After all, most of the students
that attend Ouran Academy
come from prominent families
that have their own
private doctors at home.
So this is just a formality.
These damn rich people.
I'm terribly sorry.
No problem.
Huh?
Hitachiin brothers,
would you please come with me?
We're ready to do
your chest measurements.
You can use the area behind
this curtain to undress.
Doesn't matter to me.
We're not shy.
Who needs a curtain?
See Haruhi? A rather
impressive turnout today.
Physical exam day is quite
popular with the ladies.
What's wrong with
the girls at this school?
I won't allow it,
it's just not fair.
I won't let those doctors
touch you, Kaoru.
What are you talking about?
You don't seem to have
a problem touching me
when we play doctor
at home. I can't get you to
stop tickling me
and toying with my body.
Come on, Haru-chan! This way!
W-what?
I've been waiting
for you, my princess.
Tamaki-senpai.
You're so cute
when you're surprised!
Mr. Fuijoka?
It's time for us to take
your chest measurements.
Once you've finished disrobing,
would you please come with me?
Haruhi's coming up next!
This is it, the inevitable
moment has arrived.
You just stay back here
and wait, okay Haruhi?
But what are you gonna do?
Don't you worry,
I'll protect you.
I promise I'll
protect you Haruhi.
Mr. Fujioka? Are you ready
to be measured now?
Yes.
I'm Haruhi Fujioka.
Wait. That's Tamaki!
There's no denying it.
That's definitely Tamaki.
Is he cosplaying as Haruhi?
What's going on?
Is he trying to be funny?
I can't believe
he actually did it!
They recognized him.
I told you they'd
see through it!
It's payback for calling us the
"homosexual supporting cast".
I'm sorry. They figured it out.
Just as I thought.
Tamaki-senpai lives in his
own carefree, little world.
Haruhi, ready?
I went ahead and set up
a separate room for you,
a special boys' clinic.
And I have a doctor standing
by sworn to secrecy.
It turns out the doctors
here today are all on staff
at one of Kyoya-senpai's
family's hospitals.
Would've been nice
if he had said something
to us earlier.
I had to get my revenge,
too. I'm sorry,
I just don't think I'm
supporting cast, homosexual
or otherwise.
Is there something wrong?
Check it out!
Tamaki is eroding away!
Oh wow!
Haruhi is angry with me.
Come in.
Hello Mr. Fujioka.
I've been made aware
of your situation.
If you wouldn't mind, please
disrobe for me over there.
Sure.
I'm telling the truth!
One of the doctors grabbed
me by my shoulder.
He was trying
to make a pass at me!
I've never been so terrified!
Wow, how scary!
Do you think it
was a pervert?
I had a feeling
this might happen.
What do you mean?
A bit earlier today
I saw a strange man wearing
a white lab coat but clearly
not one of our hospital's
doctors and I thought
he was a little odd.
Shouldn't you have said
something sooner?
Oh, well it's no big deal.
I'm sure the security
guard will catch him.
Tell me miss, did you
happen to notice where
the pervert doctor
was headed?
Yes, sir.
He ran off toward the
special boys' clinic.
Haruhi!
'Scuse me.
No, it's not what you think!
Please just keep quiet!
Haruhi!
Tama-chan kick!
One. Good looks that
attract the public eye.
Two. More wealth
than you can imagine.
Three.
A chivalry that will never
be able to overlook--
--the hideous wickedness
of this world.
That's what makes up
the Ouran Host Club.
We're here, watch out!
Please don't hurt me!
Spare me my life!
I'm a doctor. I have a small
emergency medical clinic
that I run in the next town
over. My name is Yabu.
Did he say his name's Yabu?
That's crazy! What a
terrible name for a doctor.
Unless you're a quack.
I know, I'm here because
I was hoping to see
my daughter. My wife
left me last month and took
my daughter with her.
But I know that she attends
school here.
I don't mean to pry
or anything but
why did your wife
and daughter leave you?
Well, you see--
"I'm sick of this!
You let someone give you
an I-owe-you again?
You promised us you wouldn't
do that anymore!"
Don't worry, dear. I know
this guy's good for it.
We can trust him.
Everything'll be alright.
"I can't take this anymore!
Dad, you never think about
the welfare of our family!"
"I'm going home to Mother!"
No! Please, wait!
And that was it.
They left me forever.
I know I'm terrible
at managing our money and
I can't say no to anybody.
I don't blame them
for being tired of
constantly living in debt.
But I wanted to see my
daughter one more time,
so I came here. After
being pelted by rain and
wandering the streets I finally
made it to your school.
Once I entered I was
mistaken for a doctor here
to examine students.
Well, of course,
you're wearing a lab coat.
Anyone would mistake you.
And then it happened.
Excuse me, miss.
I'm looking for my daughter.
When I tried to ask her
about my daughter
the girl started screaming
and before I knew it there
were all kinds of
people chasing me!
That's so tragic!
Doctor Yabu, I think you
may have the wrong place.
Are you looking for
Ouran Public High School?
Yeah that's right.
I figured that
might be the case.
This is Ouran Academy,
a private institution.
Your daughter doesn't
go to school here.
Man, that's pretty sad.
You don't even know what
school your daughter goes to?
I bet your relationship
is messed up because
you don't pay
attention to her.
Not because of
some stupid debt.
Wow Kyo-chan!
I'm impressed that
you figured out
he had the wrong school.
Well, there's no way
the daughter of such
a small-time doctor would
ever be able to get into
Ouran Academy.
Kyoya would you please
find a map of all
the public schools
in this area?
I'd like to help this man
find his daughter.
Whatever you say.
Are you sure about this?
After all, even if he does
manage to find his daughter,
there's no guarantee
she'll want to speak to him.
Well then, that's something
he'll have to find out
for himself.
I'm sorry about this you guys
but could you please leave?
Haruhi! Are you
still angry with me?
You're not thinking of quitting
the Host Club, are you?
Don't be stupid, Senpai,
I've just got to finish
my physical exam.
As a male student, of course.
But lemme explain.
I'm not doin' this cause
you're bribing me with food.
I'm doin' it to
pay back my debt.
You're so cute, Haruhi!
I can see right through you!
I know you're just after
that fancy tuna.
But it's so cute--
Cut it out,
Tamaki-senpai! Hey!
Don't touch me there!
Red card!
Looks like Tamaki senpai--
--is the real pervert!
Who cares?
Would you guys
just get out of here?
Hey Senpai, I heard a rumor
that there's another girl
joining the Host Club.
Is that true?
Don't act so surprised.
I've heard that she's
actually Kyoya's fiancée.
Next time,
Attack of the Lady Manager!
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!