Can you tell?
Which of us is Kaoru?
And which of us is Hikaru?
Well, I think you're Hikaru.
The two of us
were always together.
We were like a single entity;
a unique being.
And that closeness was
very important to us.
However, we knew we were
in fact, separate beings.
The one that was
not me was Hikaru.
And the one that was
not Hikaru was me.
For us, this concept
was something that was--
Look's like she's here.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry, were
you waiting long?
I read your letter.
Hikaru.
I'm really sorry, but--
I am Kaoru.
You must've gotten my desk
confused with Hikaru's
and you put your letter
in the wrong one.
Do you think that--You
could like me instead?
I should confess, to be
honest, I've always thought
that you were really cute.
And besides, Hikaru has
a crush on someone else.
So, what do you say?
Uh well, I-I guess.
If you're okay with it
then I am too, Kaoru.
I see. Then, hey Kaoru!
She says that she'd
be fine with you instead.
Hold on, so then
you are Hikaru?
This is getting old. You girls
just keep falling for it.
You jerk! Why're you so mean?
No, you're the one who's mean.
You're okay with
either of us? Really?
Who do you think you are?
By the way, that hairstyle
doesn't look so great
on you.
If you wanna go out
with us you should work on
your fashion sense.
And next time you write
a love letter make it good!
They're pretty mean,
aren't they?
Are you all right,
beautiful, young lady?
Hey Kaoru,
you wanna play a game?
Check it out,
I found a cool site.
Why don't we play
that game on the net?
Those guys are all
a bunch of pansies.
They're too easy to beat.
What's the fun in that?
Yeah, that's true. Nevermind.
Whenever something
got to be boring,
we'd ditch it. That's
just how we did things.
Man, those Hitachiin twins
are pretty intimidating.
Yeah, it's like they're always
looking down on everyone.
But my dad wants me to
at least try and be friends
with them.
Yeah, mine too.
Same here.
But why even bother?
I don't think those two
like anybody other than
the themselves.
That wasn't entirely true.
There was one person we were
very fond of. A maid
who took care of us.
We adored her.
But that was
a very long time ago.
Aw, look at you!
You two look so cute today!
Just like little dolls.
Now the twin with blue hair
is Hikaru and the twin
with pink hair is Kaoru, right?
No, you're wrong, Auntie.
Kaoru's blue and Hikaru's pink.
You always get it wrong.
You must be dumb.
I'm sorry, boys.
It's just that,
you two look so much alike!
And you know what you
look like to us, Auntie?
A frog!
Oh no! You little
troublemakers!
I'm so sorry, madam!
We really liked that maid.
She was different.
She didn't try
to flatter us or win us over
like everyone else
in the house did.
What are you two doing here?
We're night exploring.
Well now that
you've found me out--
I guess, I have to
make sure you stay quiet.
If we push this button--
--all of the security
guards will come running.
Should we try?
Ready. Set.
No! Don't do it!
We have the combination
for that safe.
If you'll play with us
for a little while--
--we'll give you
this piece of paper.
Fine, so what would
you like to play?
Let's play the
"which one is Hikaru?" game!
Hikaru, you sure the paper
with the combination is safe?
Don't worry. I hid it
in our piggy bank.
She can't get it out
unless she breaks it.
All we wanted was
for her to be able to tell
the two of us apart.
We really liked
that maid.
Why did you break
your promise?
Sorry boys but
I didn't have a choice.
I can't tell you two apart.
You're identical. You know,
it's possible that no one
will ever be able
to tell which one's which.
That maid, the only
person we ever liked,
dropped that bomb on us
and then disappeared
into the night.
After that we became
progressively more twisted
as we grew up.
And so we built up
a barrier to keep others from
getting too close to us.
But regardless, there was
always someone too dense
to notice the barrier
that would come along
and try to befriend us.
You have plenty
of free time, huh?
I have an idea! Why don't
you help me form a club?
Who the hell is this guy?
Oh. I know who he is.
The girls in class
were talking about him.
You know, he's that
Suou kid that was admitted
spring semester.
Oh yeah. So this
is the guy, huh?
Yeah! You know me? I had
no idea I was so famous!
Oh my, I guess I'm guilty!
I should have known my internal
and external brilliance
would blind my peers!
But I can't help
but be radiant!
So, is this the fate
of God's chosen one?
His beautiful, blessed child?
Where'd you get
an idea like that?
There's no need to be
concerned about it.
Although you're
not yet up to my level,
the two of you do show
quite a bit of promise.
What are you talking about?
I'm founding a new club
two months from now.
In April.
Ideally I would like it to
begin as soon as I graduate
into Ouran's High School.
It might be difficult
at first because you'd have to
come up from the
middle school for
the next year.
But I'm sure I can put in
a good word for you
and work it out.
It's going to be a lot of fun!
I've already asked Kyoya Otori
from my class to join.
I'm sure you know him.
And I'm also asking
high school First Years
Haninozuka-senpai and
Morinozuka-senpai
to join us.
That's where you two come in.
You're bugging us. Get lost.
We don't hang out with anyone.
And we certainly don't
wanna hang out with you.
But if you're absolutely
determined to get to know
the two of us--
--we should play--
--the "which one of us
is Hikaru?" game! You in?
The rules of the game
are pretty easy.
You just have to pick
which one of us is Hikaru.
And we'll give you one month.
You can guess as many times
as you want in that month
but we'll ask
for your reasoning.
So no random guessing.
For the record, no one has ever
been able to get it right.
If that's all right
with you then try your best.
Looks like he can't handle it.
Who cares about him?
Did you hear that lineup?
It's obvious why he wants
to add the Hitachiin name.
Its like he's gathering the
kids of high-class families.
I've got one month, right?
Then I accept. But in return,
if I win, you both have
to join my club.
Sorry to break it to you but
there's no doubt in my mind--
-come April, you're both
going to be members.
I am certain of it!
Our game had commenced.
The clock was ticking.
Um, Hikaru, Kaoru, we're
planning a special class event
after this year's
closing ceremonies.
Whatever, I think we'll pass.
But, it's going to be the last
event of our second year.
You know, we really don't care.
The one reading
the book is Hikaru!
Hang on, you can't
barge into our classroom.
But was I right?
I was right, huh?
No, you weren't. Sorry.
But I've made a discovery!
Hikaru is right-handed!
Yeah, well we're
both right-handed.
Oh yeah? Well, Kaoru always
parts his hair on the right.
No, we switch parts every day.
When you're harmonizing,
the low part goes to-
What are we, a choir?
Um, excuse me. You're
Suou-senpai, aren't you?
That's correct, my dear.
I interrupted you, didn't I?
Um no.Well, I--I was just
inviting the twins to come
to a class event.
You're going to a film
festival, huh? How nice.
I'll put them
down as attending.
They'll be there.
Hey, that's our decision!
What are you doing?
Leaving. You're annoying.
Hey wait! What about our game?
You're not bad Suou.
But you're gonna
have to try harder.
I thought you went
to go see the twins today.
I did but they ran away.
Can't blame them.
Would you help me
out here, Kyoya?
It's for the club!
Let it go. I mean, we can still
form the club without them,
right?
No, we can't! I want them
to be a part of it!
Let me guess, they're also what
you refer to as "our friends,"
is that it?
Well, yeah.
I don't understand what
they're thinking. If they
want people to tell them
apart, why don't they
wear different
hairstyles or something?
Maybe they don't
want to be told apart.
But that's the whole
point of the game, Kyoya.
Well, then they do
want to be told apart.
Hold on. Are you
even listening to me?
Well, I hear you talking.
Today Kaoru's hair is parted
on the right and Hikaru's
is on the left!
Good morning Hitachiin twins!
What do you want? You can't
just show up like this.
Am I right?
Did I get it right?
No, you couldn't be more wrong.
But I've made a discovery!
Kaoru, you're pigeon-toed,
aren't you?
You should fix that.
That's not true! How rude!
I came up with an idea
last night. We can focus
on your brotherly love
and make that your draw!
A somewhat taboo and
perfectly symmetrical
brotherly love.
The Hitachiin Brothers!
So what do you think?
You don't make any sense.
Wait! Don't run away again!
Come back here!
What the hell is with that guy?
I can't believe
he showed up at our place.
You know, when he
gets all dramatic--
Oh yeah! I thought so too.
He sounds like
some feudal lord!
I never thought I'd see a young
prince character like him
use that tone of voice!
"Come back here!" he said!
"Come back here!"
I bet pretty soon he'll
start talking in third person!
A feudal lord! What an clown!
But then again.
This game's getting
kinda boring.
Like we said, we're done.
Game over.
What are you talking about?
You're calling it off?
We can do whatever we want.
That's right.
'Cause we heard you're
the illegitimate son
of Ouran's chairman.
Sorry to be so blunt but we
did a little research on you.
You've got quite a sad,
little, life story Suou.
I'm sure you wouldn't
want us passing
that information along.
We found out that your
real mother has gone missing.
Be honest, you're just
lonesome because you're
all by yourself, right?
We feel kinda sorry for you
but you can't force us
to be your friends.
We are pretty lonely but
at least we have each other,
that's more than you.
Hikaru, c'mon.
'kay.
He won't go sticking his nose
into our business anymore.
But you know,
it's kind of a shame.
We probably could've played
the game a little longer.
But-- I'm not up for being
disappointed, not again.
We were always
contradicting ourselves.
We wanted to be told apart.
We didn't want
to be told apart.
We wanted people to know us.
We didn't want them to know.
We were always looking
for someone who would
finally accept us.
But there was no way
that would ever happen,
not as twisted as we were.
We were so afraid of
someone breaking through
our barrier and hurting us.
We kept a strong
lock on our hearts
to protect ourselves.
Hey, Kaoru?
She's here.
Yeah, you're right.
I see. Then, Hikaru!
She says she'd
be fine with you instead.
Oh well, should've known.
You may have a sweet
and pretty face but you're
a terrible person, you know.
By saying you'll
take either of us--
--you're really saying
you don't want either of us.
You're mean!
No, you've got it
all wrong, you're mean.
The one about to
rip the letter is Hikaru!
But how did you know?
Am I right? Did I get it right?
Your reasoning?
Intuition!
No way. I thought
we already told you that
you weren't allowed
to just guess randomly.
Yeah, sorry about that.
But it's still to early for me
to tell. I mean, you are
both totally identical.
But it all depends on
how you choose to look at it.
Being so identical is
a talent in and of itself.
So from now on, you should
try to perfect the whole
"two-in-one Hitachiin
Brothers" act.
But you mustn't forget
that you're also
independent beings with
your own personalities.
And while you're doing that--
I'll keep bugging you
until I can tell you apart.
That doesn't make any sense!
It's contradictory!
And what's wrong with that?
Haven't you realized yet?
You two are contradictory.
It's what they call
"individuality."
What are you talking about?
If we play along with this
silly "Hitachiin Brothers"
act like you want us to,
you'll never tell up apart-
we'll be even more identical!
You didn't think
about that, did you?
How can we show our
"individuality" if no one
can tell us apart?
It's always like this-
we're the only ones who
can tell the difference!
No one will ever
be able to win the
"which one is Hikaru?" game.
And we've known that
from the beginning!
Then why don't
you tell me something?
When someone guesses wrong,
why do you look so sad?
And then, I remembered.
Well, I think you're Hikaru.
You guessed wrong.
And after that,
the little girl said.
I'm so sorry, please don't cry.
I remembered how surprised
I was when I heard
her say those words.
In fact, I bet we
both looked like
we were about to
cry at that moment.
Even though I may not be able
to, someday, somewhere,
someone's going
to come along who
can tell the two of you apart.
But I know this much
for sure. If you guys keep
living in your
own little world like
you do now,
chances are you're never
going to meet that person.
Here's what I think,
we should open the doors
of the Host Club together!
Let's try to expand
your world, together.
Our first meeting will
be after opening ceremonies
on the first day
of school. It'll be
in music room 3
in the high school.
That day, we were amazed.
He had answered correctly.
And subconsciously
we were a little bit,
just a little bit,
impressed with him.
Wow, this school's incredible!
If I am admitted,
am I even gonna be able
to handle it here?
I see. So, Suou invited you
to join the club too, Takashi?
Yeah.
Know what he said?
He told me it's perfectly okay
for me to like cute
stuff and that I can
eat all the cake
that I want.
Now I don't know
what I should do.
Do whatever you want,
Mitsukuni.
It's no big deal.
Okay! Sounds like a plan!
Yeah, I think I can manage it.
I just have to pass
the entrance exams.
Remember Kaoru,
we can't let ourselves be
moved by what that
foolish lord says.
Yeah, I know. We're just
here to kill some time.
Right, that's it.
We're just killing time.
You're identical.
You know, it's possible that
no one will ever
be able to tell
which one's which.
You were right, lady.
There's no one in this world
who can tell
the two of us apart.
No one at all.
I know that for a fact
but even so--
Let's open the doors together.
Ready, set--
And so we opened the door.
"The Door the Twins Opened"
Starting today, the Host Club
is having a special
Halloween week!
We're sorry, boss.
But we're going to miss it.
We have a class event.
Hey, wait up! Are you
taking Haruhi with you?
Next time, "Until the Day
it Becomes a Pumpkin!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you.
We'll see you then!