Really? All the afternoon
classes have been cancelled?
You mean, no one told you?
It's going to be crazy around
here for the next two days.
Ouran is hosting an exposition
for the cultural clubs.
Drama and choir clubs from
a bunch of other schools have
been invited. It's a big event
the school hosts annually.
Is that so?
What?! You've never tried it?!
Didn't anyone tell you that
it's the preferred drink
of the Host Club?
And you are our manager
so you should drink it too.
Um, well I-I think I've heard
of instant coffee before.
Oh! That's right! Isn't that
when the coffee beans have
already been ground for you?
That's just ground coffee,
instant is something completely
different. I don't even think
there are any coffee beans
in instant coffee. You just mix
this powder with hot water and
then drink it- you don't have
to brew it. It's pretty awesome.
So it's basically just like
coffee but not as robust.
And yet, it's
strangely satisfying.
Now that you mention it we
just ran out of it, didn't we?
Go buy us some more, Haruhi.
Why do I have to go get it?
Because you're the only
commoner no one else knows
where to buy it.
We've even been serving it to
our guests lately and besides,
it's part of your job.
But the cultural club
exposition starts soon.
Yeah, but it's not mandatory
so if you're not interested
you don't have to go.
And with that being said.
Be careful out there!
Damn them.
I really hate rich people.
Thanks for
helping them out, Haruhi.
No problem. I just wish they'd
buy their own instant coffee.
Well, I don't know if that'll
ever happen but I'm glad
they seem to be
having a good time.
And it's all thanks to you,
All thanks to me?
We've been in the same class
as the twins ever since
middle school.
They didn't used to be this
cheerful and friendly. They were
always quiet and withdrawn-
they didn't have many friends.
It's like they didn't want
anyone to get too close.
I don't think they liked
school very much they seemed
so bored by it.
I guess things started to change
when the host club was created.
Since then, they've come out of
their shells little by little.
Really?
But they've really opened
up since you've joined
the host club, Now they talk and
joke with everyone in class.
That's why we wanted
to make sure you knew how
grateful we are to you. Because
of you the twins are having fun
and enjoying each day
to the fullest.
It'd be a shame for any harm to
come to that cute face of yours.
Young lady.
A Challenge From
Lobelia Girls Academy!
This looks like the place.
Mm-hmm.
Welcome, ladies!
Well, well, well, I see you
ladies are from another school.
I certainly hope
we haven't startled you.
We love first-time guests.
I'm glad you've come,
princesses. My darlings,
even if the world were to be
destroyed, I'd put my life
on the line as your faithful
knight and servant.
I will protect you.
Oh my, do you really think
you'd be able to protect us?
That's awfully arrogant of you,
wouldn't you agree?
You think that's what
a woman wants to hear?
Well, you're wrong.
C'mon, give him a break,
Sister Suzuran.
Men are just lowly life forms
who don't care about
anything other than perpetuating
their testosterone-laden image.
By "protecting us" he is
actually attempting to disguise
the fact that he
is weak and unable
of even protecting himself.
You're such
a clever girl, Hinagiku.
Don't you think
that's a little harsh?
Fine then, what do women
like you want to hear?
Maybe something like, "I would
never leave my lover alone."
"If we fight, it'll be together.
If we fail, we fail together."
"Even if I were to die,
I promise you that I will never
leave your side, my love."
Benibara, we thought
you'd never show.
What are we going
to do with you?
So tell us where you found
this lovely young lady.
I just met her
outside of the school.
She may be dressed as
a boy but I knew the truth.
She has such pretty,
maidenly eyes.
Uh, thanks, I guess?
Wow, her skin
is incredibly soft.
Isn't it, though?
I think this one's going to be
a little diamond in the rough.
Don't go touching my Haruhi
without asking my permission!
Leave her alone!
She punched me!
She's so violent!
Get a hold of yourself!
Guess the rumors
we heard are true.
You guys are just a bunch
of weak little punks with
no sense between you.
Those uniforms.
I assume you ladies are from
the Lobelia Girls' Academy?
That's correct.
Lobelia!
St. Lobelia Academy, high
school 2nd-Year, Benio Amakusa.
Lobelia.
2nd-Year student,
Chizuraru Maihara.
Lobelia.
1st-Year student,
Hinako Tsuwabuki.
Lobelia.
We are the members
of St. Lobelia Academy's
white lily league
also known as--
The Zuka Club!
The Zuka Club?
Oh man, what a stupid name!
The Zuka Club! My stomach hurts!
The Zuka Club! That's priceless!
And they had those get-ups
on under their uniforms!
You shouldn't
underestimate the Zuka Club!
I may not know much
about instant coffee but
I'm fascinated
with girls' schools.
St. Lobelia Academy! It is
truly a woman's world there.
The Zuka club is a group
of strong young maidens
who consider women
to be superior in every way.
The club prides itself
on its 30 year history.
It's a society of maidens,
by maidens, for maidens.
Zuka Club activities include:
"Maiden Tea Parties",
"The Maiden Debate Forum", and
most importantly musical reviews
performed by the
society's top members.
You sure have a vast wealth
of knowledge, Renge.
Well, I've always
admired St. Lobelia's.
I just couldn't go to school
there though- what would I do
without any boys?
A maiden's beauty.
It means possessing a spirit
pure enough to not give in
to power or to lust.
"As a girl, you"
"for a girl, you"
We've had quite enough
of all your oppressive
male contempt for woman-kind.
And our pride.
Comes from having meaningful
relationships based on
equality because
we're the same sex.
And yes, that includes
relationships of love.
Yeah, You tell them, Benio.
You're awesome, Benibara!
Whatever. We're so over it.
Why don't you gals just scram?
I find it hard to believe
that you silly boys
have nothing to say about
our sublime female love.
What the hell
is she talking about?
Hey, I haven't seen this one
before. I guess it's a new one.
You should feel
sorry for them, Hinagiku.
Their patented host skills
didn't work on us-
now they're all flustered
and they don't know
what to do with themselves.
True, I must say I'm glad
we decided to perform here.
It was fun to sneak a peek at
the notorious Ouran Host Club.
Hey guys, are we
really notorious?
Yeah.
And to think they're
dragging this sweet young girl
down with them.
The host club's president
may be a pretty little halfer.
But he shouldn't be using
his looks to create
a fictitious romance! Attempting
to fool the heart of a pure,
young maiden is demeaning!
Your so-called "club activities"
are nothing more
than debasing macho fantasies.
I promise you, we will
bring you guys down.
The Ouran Host Club
will be abolished!
All hail Zuka Club!
I see. I understand your
concern, but do you think
maybe we could
finish this later?
Are you saying that
you're not going to face us?
Not at all.
It's just that our president
is still bedridden
from the initial culture shock.
You see Tama-chan is having
his nappy time right now.
Wake him up!
'Scuse me. I made some coffee,
would you ladies like some?
Why, yes! Aren't you
the sweetest thing?
You're a real pearl
among swine!
You know, coffee made
by a maiden always has
a more fragrant aroma.
But this stuff's just instant.
How about the four of us
have a little tea party?
You girls have it all wrong!
Don't you see there's
nothing to be gained
in a romantic relationship
between two women?!
If that were the case then
why did God create
Adam and Eve?!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
You gotta be
more careful, senpai.
Thanks, Haruhi. Do you always
carry bandages around with you?
Nah. The supermarket
was giving 'em out with
the purchase of instant coffee.
You always get free stuff
at the supermarket.
Free stuff?
This little conversation doesn't
seem to be going anywhere.
Now that we know what's
going on, we can't allow this
maiden to stay here.
We'll prepare her paperwork and
have her transferred
to Lobelia at once.
And we'll welcome her
into the Zuka Club!
Hey, just wait
a second, will ya?
There seem to have been some
misunderstandings here.
I mean, first of all,
you called Tamaki a "halfer".
Cause he is a halfer. He's
half French and half Japanese!
Well, uh, anway, I don't think
it's fair for you to pick on
the host club just because
you don't think they have
the same history you do.
We barely have any history-
we were just founded
two years ago.
Yeah, The boss
created it whenever
he started high school here.
Be that as it may, saying their
club activities are only held
to satisfy their appetites is
just wrong. I mean, it's not
like the host club is charging
their guests or anything.
While I wouldn't call
it a charge we do have
a point system. We offer
priority services based on
the winning bids of auctions
held on our website.
Check this out, Haruhi. Your
used mechanical pencil just sold
with a winning bid of
30,000 yen. Good for you.
What?! But I thought
I'd lost that pencil!
Why didn't you tell me about
this before, Kyoya-senpai?!
I had no idea you
were collecting money!
So, you thought we were all just
working here as volunteers?
While it's not much
because of the expense
of organizing events,
we happen to make a small profit
from the online auctions.
You can't go selling
people's things without
asking their permission!
That's stealing!
It wasn't stealing you dropped
your pencil on the floor.
I'm sorry, Haruhi! It's not like
we were hiding it from you!
Here, you can have mine! It's
got a cute teddy bear on it!
Senpai, I don't want you pencil.
Then to make it up to you
how about I do this.
I'll tell you the secrets to my
success and my fondest memories.
Not to be rude senpai,
but I'm really not interested
in that information.
Not interested?
Oh you poor dear.
I can't believe they've
been deceiving you.
Hey, why don't you just dump
these losers and come with us?
Hold on, Hinagiku. This young
maiden has had quite a day.
We'll give you some time
to think about it.
We'll come back
for your answer tomorrow.
Well then.
Adieu.
I'd better be going.
I've got some thinking to do.
Why did you have
to tell her the truth?!
You just added fuel to the fire!
What am I going to do now?
The facts are the facts.
Maybe we should've
asked before we sold
her pencil on the internet.
Yeah, for all we know it was
a keepsake from her mother.
Nah, it was just a freebie
they were giving out
at an electronics store.
Gentlemen, just think about it.
Haruhi may be
basically indifferent,
but if she had to choose
we know that she tends
to favor men's clothing. And
besides, when she first joined
the Host Club
didn't she tell us-
Being a host and getting
fussed over by a bunch of girls
might not be that bad.
Why didn't I realize this
before? Perhaps they would be
a better match for Haruhi.
Maybe she'd be better off.
With the Zuka Club.
Yeah, she's perfect
for a girl's school.
Haru-chan is going to
transfer away!
What are we going to do?
Haruhi's so smart, passing
Lobelia's scholarship test
will be a piece of cake!
And Lobelia Academy
has the money to pay off
the 8 million yen debt
she owes us.
Calm down, gentlemen.
It'll be alright.
Listen to what I have to say.
I have a secret plan.
Lo!
Bel!
I!
A!
Ah!
I thought today's performance
went extremely well.
Our singing and acting skills
are admired wherever we go.
That's true, but the main event
has yet to begin, right girls?
Hi, young maiden.
We've come for your decision,
are you prepared to leave?
We're ready to confront
those Ouran Host Club idiots
and set things straight
once and for all.
Set what straight?
That you should come with us.
And go to school
with your own kind!
Ouran!
Host Club!
Welcomes you!
Oh, Haruhi, welcome back.
Look Haru-chan! I'm a
princess now! Aren't I cute?!
What is the meaning of this?!
Are you trying to make
fun of woman kind?!
Make fun? No,
that's not it at all.
Everything's going
according to plan.
Our strategy is guaranteed to
make even a crying child smile;
it's the Freebie Campaign!
My dears, you ladies have
all lived sheltered lives
at Lobelia, so you might not
know that commoners are weak.
They have a weakness
for free things.
Haruhi, you may be
distracted by the Zuka Club,
but choose us.
And you gain not only
a host club full of brothers
but sisters as well!
See? This way you can
experience feminine bonding
while staying in the host club!
Isn't that a great idea?!
Aren't I pretty?
We're the Hitachin Sisters!
Which one of us is prettier?
I'm just teasing you.
Listen Haru-chan!
You can call me
Big Sis from now on.
Why you! Do you idiots
really think you can
win her over like this? I've had
enough of your fooling around!
This is too much!
I don't even get what you
guys are tryin' to do!
I know you're a bunch
of goofballs but geez!
Are we really that funny?
Call me Big Sister! C'mon do
it! Just say it! Big Sister!
Say it, please?!
Come on, cut it out!
What were you thinking?
What's gotten into you guys?
We did this because
we don't want you
to leave the host club, Haruhi.
Well, maiden,
have you made a choice?
Yeah, I have. I'm sorry
but your club's not for me.
I think the idea of a
girl's school is great and
I think your views are very
unique and interesting.
But I came to this school with
a goal and a plan for my future-
so while I appreciate the offer,
I really already knew
that I was never going
to leave Ouran Academy.
Haruhi!
Hold on! If you knew
you weren't going to leave
then why did you act
so angry yesterday?
How would you feel if
I stole something of yours
without asking you?! I really
liked that mechanical pencil
it was easy to write with!
I'm sorry, but I was nice and
offered you my teddy bear pencil
in return and you said
you didn't want it!
That's right and
I still don't want it.
Um, Benio.
Yes... I know.
We're not going to
give up on you, maiden.
I swear this to you.
Someday we'll come and
rescue you from this place!
And when we do we'll abolish
the Ouran Host Club!
Well, Adieu!
And so a new rival, the
Zuka Club, has appeared.
From this point on the story's
gonna get even more exciting!
What's gonna happen to our
beloved host club boys next?
Hang in there, Host Club!
Don't give up, boys!
Hey! It's not your job
to cook things up!
Is Haruhi really suffering
in a life of poverty?!
I have to go see for myself!
You're just gonna cause trouble.
You don't need to come over.
Whoa, you're Haruhi's father?
Next time, "A Day in the Life
of the Fujioka Family!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!