Welcome to the Host Club.
What are these things
all over the room?
Are they furniture?
If my memory
serves me correctly,
they're called kotatsu.
Oh, I wondered what
those looked like.
I've never seen one before.
Neither have I.
Indeed it is a kotatsu,
normally they're only used
in the winter.
It may be a little early in
the season for one of these
but I figured it was
perfect for you ladies.
After all, you're always one
step ahead of the crowd,
aren't you?
Now my darlings. I hope
that you will enjoy today's
home-style kotatsu service,
presented by our Host Club.
I never really thought of
sitting under a kotatsu as fun.
Well, the ladies
seem to enjoy it.
Let me guess, this
kotatsu service is one
of Tamaki-senpai's
ideas, isn't it?
Yeah.
What's the matter? Do you have
something against kotatsus?
Not at all, I was just
thinking about something.
Now correct me if I'm
wrong but the Host Club
was originally founded by both
you and Tamaki-senpai, right?
That is correct.
Okay, well here's what I don't
get. Why would somebody
as cool as you fall
for a crazy idea like
a high school host club?
Well, Because it was
a crazy idea.
Back then the third son of
the Ootori family was about
to begin his final spring
in middle school.
And so Kyoya met him.
Kyoya Ootori!
Kyoya, wait up!
What's up? My dad
told me he went to the
completion commemoration
for your family's
new hospital yesterday.
He was totally surprised! He
said it was like a who's who
of the top people
in every field!
He asked me to be sure
to tell you thank you.
This is the son of the chairman
of a major electronics company.
It's no big deal. I hope
you'll be able to attend
the next one with your father.
Hey Kyoya!
We just heard that you're at
the head of the class again.
This is the son of a major
department store family.
And you're gonna be
class rep again for the
3rd Year in a row,
how cool!
And this is the youngest son
of a well-known Diet member.
Whoa, look over there!
It's Kyoya!
He looks so handsome!
Yeah he does.
And these are some
frivolous-minded girls.
Hey, Ootori!
How'd you like to come
visit my family's villa
in the mountains?
This one's the son of a
prestigious funds manager.
You guys can come too.
It's beautiful up there
you can see so many stars!
We even built
a small observatory.
My father likes to use
the villa for vacations
so we might see him
while we're there.
I couldn't care less
about stargazing.
That sounds like
a great idea.
--but I'm very interested
in meeting your father.
My, my, my Kyoya.
You're really going to impose
on their vacation just
to meet his father?
I'm not imposing.
I was invited. He asked me
to join him at the villa.
It's simply a give-and-take
situation Sis.
Why does everything have
to be so manipulative
with you? Did you think that
maybe they honestly just
wanted you to come look
at the stars with them?
I think it's really sweet.
Two young men bonding
underneath the stars.
Fuyumi would you
please stop it.
I've asked you a million
times to stop rummaging
through my drawers like that.
What was that? Uh, I'm
not rummaging I'm just
trying to organize
all of your clothes
for you, Kyoya.
It won't go back in
I know it--
Why don't you just let
the maid take care of that?
Listen Kyoya.
I know dad's really strict and
he puts a lot of pressure
on you but you're different
than our older brothers.
Remember, he doesn't expect
as much from you.
So it's okay if you
take it easy sometimes.
I know. I'll never be successor
of the Ootori family.
I'm not like my brothers. All
they had to do was follow
the path that they
had been promised.
A path that keeps heading
upward. It's because
I'm the third son
that I can't relax.
I'll surpass father's
expectations of me and I will
respect my brothers
and never step on
their toes in the process.
How can I demonstrate my
abilities without exceeding
the limits of being
the "third son"?
I have a daunting task.
I must paint the
perfect picture on
a canvas that has already
been placed inside
a magnificent frame.
You're such a bright boy,
Kyoya. Everything you do,
you do exceptionally well.
But tell me will
you ever be happy?
To be honest, whether I'm
happy or unhappy has nothing
to do with it.
My oldest brother had already
graduated from medical school
and was in training
at the same hospital
as my father
as his successor.
My second brother was
still in medical school
and was planning
to get an MBA after
he graduated so he
could support our brother.
And then, there was me,
the third son.
Kyoya.
Today is the day that
Suou's son is going to be
transfering into
your class, right?
We've done business with
the Suou group for many years
now and we have a wonderful
relationship with them.
But competition is
still a possibility,
so I've been thinking.
Your befriending young Suou
would be in our
family's best interest.
But whatever you do Kyoya,
don't forget. Always keep
your friends close
and your enemies closer.
Yes sir. I remember.
Staying at the head
of the class isn't enough.
Both of your brothers did the
same when they were in school.
I'm sure you're aware that
it'll take more than that
to satisfy me.
I'm counting on you, Kyoya.
Yes sir. I know that.
I was confident that
I had the ability to see
through other people's facades
but they could never see
through mine.
It didn't matter what this
Suou guy might be like
making friends with
him would be easy.
I would do anything
that my father wanted.
Tamaki Suou. So, his son
was conceived while
the chairman was overseas.
The chairman eventually
decided to take him in
since he had no
other children and
was recently divorced.
And so the chairman's love
child becomes the heir
to the Suou group overnight.
Well isn't he a lucky fellow?
Class Representative,
vice-representative,
please come this way.
Allow me to introduce you
to our new student,
Tamaki Suou.
It's a pleasure
to meet you both.
This is class
representative Kyoya Ootori
and vice-representative
Ayame Jonouchi.
You have the most
beautiful straight hair that
I've ever seen.
I would assume that
your heart is just as
blindingly beautiful
as that hair of yours.
Maybe it's
a cultural difference?
Nice to meet you, Ootori.
The pleasure is all mine.
You know, if you'd like,
I can take you on
a tour of the school.
That'd be great.
Thank you very much.
Up ahead of us is the
west school building all
special classrooms
are on the other side.
Oh, I forgot. I was
wondering Ootori do you
have a kotatsu at your house?
Oh Surely you do. I think
kotatsus are simply amazing!
I've always thought it was
cool that the Japanese
sit on the floor.
I told myself I would
sit under one
once I got to Japan.
But at home,
the décor is all western.
Ah, so he's one of those.
There are a number of
foreigners enamoured
with Japanese culture.
Unfortunately, we don't
have any kotatsu either,
we do have Japanese
décor though.
What happened? Did I step on
a land mine or something?
I can't believe it.
You don't have a kotatsu?
I'm sorry Ootori.
It was rather insensitive
of me to ask you that.
I guess you're family isn't as
close as they could be, huh?
Look, it's okay you don't
have to hide it anymore.
I'm well aware that the
kotatsu is a symbol for
a happy home life in Japan.
Correct me if I'm wrong, but
here in Japan you playfully
kick each other's feet under the
kotatsu while building familial
bonds of trust and watching
Costume Grand Prix, right?
And of course, you also eat
plenty of mandarin oranges!
I feel sorry for you, you and
your family are missing out.
I hate to correct you but I
think you've got the wrong idea.
If its that important to you,
we can always put a kotatsu
in our home for you to visit.
Thank you Ootori! Yay!
You're such a good friend!
You're my best friend!
Hey, Ootori. I don't
wanna be too forward
or anything but since
we're pals do you think
it's okay for me to call you
by your first name?
Bravo! Kyoya! My pal!
Mon ami! Yahoo!
My, my, my Kyoya.
You became his best
friend in one day.
I don't think he even knows what
it means to be "best friends".
To be honest, I can't be
positive he's even fluent
in Japanese.
Sis, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Would you please
quit rummaging through
my drawers like that?
Today he drew me in,
got me to play everything
at his pace. Well,
at least now know he's
a complete idiot.
Kyoya, you have too many things
crammed into these drawers.
Once you pull something out,
there's no way
to get it back in.
Then don't pull anything out.
Kyoya, I need to ask
a favor of you.
You see, I really
want to go to Kyoto.
I got so excited about
the kotatsu that I forgot.
I always said that once I got
to Japan I'd go to Kyoto.
The Great Buddha at Nara.
Goryokaku Park,
I want to see Sheesa
and Namahage.
I want to see everything!
One problem none of
those things are in Kyoto.
He's an even bigger idiot
than I thought
How about we see each of
those things, one at a time?
Why don't we go to Kyoto
this weekend and then
on our next school holiday
we can go to Okeenawa.
Thank you, Kyoya!
You're the greatest! Like a
god! Like the great Buddha!
Kyoya! Mon ami! Mon ami!
Kyoya! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Again with the "mon ami"
business. It's only the
second day I've known him and
I'm already a god in his eyes.
For some reason it seems like
I just can't get my head
around this guy.
Before I knew it,
he had completely
won over our class.
Kyoya! I found a Namahage!
Namahage! Namahage!
Namahage!
No that's a Shisa.
My, my, my, Kyoya. I knew I'd
find you up late studying.
Wait a minute,
are those travel guides?
Oh wow, so you guys are
going to Hokkaido next?
That's wonderful!
But if you need a guide,
I'm sure that you could
ask the family driver.
That's not good enough not
for this Tamaki Suou guy.
When we went to Kyoto
he wanted to see the
daimoanji bonfire even though
it's still spring time and
as we were eating
Okinawa soba noodles
he tells me he wants
to compare them to
Shinshu soba noodles.
Then he went on about
whether a shisa or a namahage
would win in a fight.
And then, after all that.
I'm sorry for asking you
to do all of this.
You're right. It's not
your responsibility, Kyoya.
I'm Sorry. I've overestimated
your ability to entertain me.
But this time I'm going to make
sure I'm ready for anything!
I promise that while the two
of us are in Hokkaido,
I will cater to your
every whim, Suou!!!!
We're going to Hokkaido?
I know you want to enjoy
your life to the fullest but
don't you think
we should be spending
our time studying
for finals right now?
We can go to Hokkaido
when they're over.
I think you should start
hitting the books, my friend.
My, my, my, Kyoya.
Kyoya what on earth is
the matter with you?
That bastard!
He's an idiot. I knew that
but I honestly had
no idea that he that he was
such a total dumbass!
Next week, let's go
to Hokkaido, okay?!
I've never wanted
to hit someone so badly
in my entire life!
DAMN! I HATE HIM!
Okay, calm down.
He may be an idiot but
he is the Suou family's heir.
Getting emotional
isn't going to help anything.
Obivously father's testing my
ability to cope with
certain situations.
Even so, I won't forget
this you bastard.
Damn you, Tamaki Suou.
You really expect me
to buy a kotatsu just for you?
I was going to tell Kyoya that
if he can't stand the kid
then there's no reason to force
himself to hang out with him.
But you know, I've never seen
him so passionate about
anything before.
It's been a while since I've
had a day off from Tamaki.
Your friend has come
to visit today.
My friend?
Beautiful, isn't it?
It brings me to tears.
To be honest, the first time
I heard him play the piano
I was in complete shock.
Not because my brothers
were in tears but because
without even realizing it,
that beautiful music had
brought me to tears as well.
Sorry for just dropping
by out of the blue like this.
If that's how you feel,
then go home.
So what happened
to studying for finals?
Have you finished yet?
Wow, your house is gigantic
Kyoya! I wonder if this one
could be any bigger than my
house the one I have in France.
What're you trying to say?
Well. I don't know about
your mansion in France
but I'm sure your estate is
bigger than mine, right?
Well uh, I wouldn't know
because I've never been
in the main estate before. And
uh, the second estate is small.
So Kyoya, are you the successor
to the Ootori family estate?
Is this guy actually trying
to pick a fight with me?!
There's no way that'll
happen my brothers they're
the first in line.
I'm sure that I'll just end up
working for them someday.
Really? That's a surprise.
Maybe I'm wrong but I get
the feeling you want more
than that I mean.
When I look in your eyes
I can tell you're not happy
with your situation.
I'm surprised you'd
give up so easily.
This has nothing to do with
whether I'm giving up or not.
It's just the way things are!
You wouldn't understand
because you'll be successor
to your family's estate without
even lifting a finger.
Damn it.
Its not certain that I'll be
the Suou family successor.
My grandmother doesn't
like me. So if things
stay the way they are now
then I'm not the heir,
I'm not anything. I'm kind
of in a probationary period.
I can't believe I
didn't tell you that.
To be completely honest
with you. I'm not really
all that interested in
my father's line of work.
And besides, look at me. I can't
let these looks go to waste.
And you know, I am
incredibly smart so maybe
I could be a brilliant
scientist. You know what
I'd love to do more than
anything? I want to open
an animal kingdom in the
north. When I close my eyes
I can see it!
Shut up, Tamaki!
Do you expect me
to believe that crap?!
How can you possibly give
up on being your family's
successor so easily?!
You have no idea what it's
like for me! You actually
have a chance at it all
you have to do is try!
Take advantage of your
fortunate circumstances!
Don't you realize the position
that you've been blessed with?!
I can't believe you, damn it.
Who the hell are you?!
Of course, I know that my
brothers are no more suited
for the position
than I am, but.
I will always feel the
frustration of not being able
to step outside of my frame
because I am the third son.
Hold on. It sounds to
me like you're the one
who isn't trying.
If you really want to
surpass your brothers
then you can do it.
But I think The one who's
given up here--
is you, Kyoya.
Oh yeah and by the way
where's that kotatsu
I asked for? Not to be
a pain but I thought
you'd have it ready
for me by now that's
why I stopped by your place.
What is it? Hey,
what's so funny.
Let me guess, you've got
the kotatsu ready to go
and you're trying
to hide it from me.
It's not all about you,
you know.
Kotatsu are only used in
the winter. So if you want
to sit under one you'll
have to wait until then.
Now would you quit
being a dumb ass?
Oh man your face, it looks evil.
So you're finally showing
your true colors?
Hey Kyoya, I just had
the most brilliant idea!
We should start
a club together!
We could start our club
activities as soon
as we get into high school.
And we can finally
make use of our good looks
with a high school host club!
Sleep first and then dream.
I'm serious! I already know
who we should ask to join!
We have to ask
Haninozuka-senpai and
Morinozuka-senpai from the
high school and those
2nd Year twins.
It seemed like the more I
listened, the more ridiculous
his plans became. But for some
reason, I got the feeling
that if I shared his world. I
would experience something
different than anything I had
ever experienced before.
As a special event during the
school festival the Host Club
will be open to the public
for the next two days.
We'll entertain our guests
even more extravagantly than
we usually do.
Next time, "The Host Club
Declares Dissolution!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll See you then!