The beach?
Of course! The beach!
But why?
Don't you remember
what you said?
You said you'd like
to go to a real beach.
Did I say that?
Yes, Haruhi.
Here's the fun part!
We've brought some swimsuits
for you to choose from.
Pretty cute,
don't you think?
Not that one! I think that
this swimsuit would look
much cuter on Haru-chan.
I don't think you get it.
Honey-senpai.
Just look, this uniform barely
hides the fact that Haruhi's
as flat as a cutting board.
A one-piece suit like that
one would only upset her
because it draws attention to
her lacking feminine physique.
That's why we carefully selected
this two piece suit, see?
The ruffles help hide the fact
that she's so flat-chested!
You punks had better
quit sexually harassing
my little girl!
I've had enough of you!
That mean we're
not going to the beach?
Who said that we're not going?
Really? So you wanna
go after all?
Can Usa-chan come, too?
I have no problem with that.
Huh? We're really gonna go?
Why not? Let's go to the beach!
The Sun, the Sea,
and the Host Club!
So, why'd we come to Okinawa?
Because Kyoya's family
has a private beach here.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
But why couldn't we have gone-
-to the Caribbean?
Or even Fiji?
Do you think a commoner
like Haruhi has a passport?
Ah.
You do realize that I can hear
what you're saying, right?
It's so beautiful.
Tamaki, being alone here
with you and looking out
at the sea,
it's like a dream.
It's no dream, it's real,
but if I could have my way,
my princess.
I'd be in your dreams
every night.
Oh, Tamaki.
Hey, take it easy, Hikaru!
I'm sorry! I'll get it!
Wait for me, Kaoru!
It's not my fault!
The ball is rolling away!
Why?
Her alone time with Tamaki is
up. Next lady, please proceed.
This sucks. I thought going
to the beach meant a day off.
Um, Haruhi?
Aren't you going to
go swimming with us?
No, uh, I like looking at
the sea from a safe distance.
Well, if you're not going
to swim would you mind
if we sat here
and talked with you?
But why?
You girls should go swim.
You've got cute swim suits on;
why not show them off?
I can't believe he fooled us.
Who'd have thought he'd
bring the ladies with us?
We certainly
didn't expect it.
You were invited on this
all-expenses-paid vacation
for a reason.
And that is to keep
our clients entertained.
We know, but with
the ladies here-
-Haruhi can't change
into her swimsuit.
Don't worry- I've got it
all under control.
My little angel shouldn't be
prancing around in a swimsuit,
at least not in front
of two perverts like you.
And then, once the sun has
begun to set. Haruhi and I
will take a romantic stroll
along the shore together.
Oh wow, what a pretty sunset.
Oh, senpai, I'd love to be
with you here forever!
It'll happen just like that!
The greatest day of my life!
I don't know if
I can handle it!
What's the matter with Tamaki-
is he having a seizure?
I wouldn't worry about it.
He gets like this occasionally.
Haru-chan!
Wanna go hellfish shunting?!
I think you're trying to say
"shellfish hunting".
But this doesn't seem to
be that kind of beach,
Honey-senpai. You're not going
to find many shellfish here.
What the hell?! No way!
One, two, one, two.
Mori-senpai.
My family's private
police force has stopped by.
They wanted to make it up to
Honey-senpai for attacking him
at the water park.
So they've brought shellfish.
Amazing! Look
how many we've got!
We're gonna have some
fancy side dishes tonight!
It's gonna be delicious!
My, my, certainly looks like
they're enjoying themselves,
all is right with the world.
Senpai!
Dinner is gonna be awesome!
It's a major haul!
Oh, I'm just so proud!
Look at my little girl!
It's a major haul!
Say what?
Dinner is gonna be awesome!
It'll be a real treat!
Tell me Haruhi? Don't you think
Isn't this crab-Crab-tivating?
Oh yeah!
You're so cute.
Cen.
Ti.
Pede!
Hey, Haruhi.
Now, I know most girls aren't
really the bug-loving type
and I certainly didn't
think you were but-
-don't you think you could've
been easier on that little guy?
Oh c'mon it's not dead.
It takes a lot more than that
to kill a bug.
Haruhi is so brave and manly.
But still so sweet.
He's the best!
Well, isn't that just great.
Haruhi's not normal. I thought
girls were afraid of bugs.
I'm sure she's
afraid of something.
Hey, Boss! Listen up!
We just thought up
a new game to play that
could be a lot of fun.
What do you say?
It's called the "Who can find
out Haruhi's weakness game"!
So, think you're up to it?
But that game sounds terrible.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Besides, she'd only
share her weakness with
someone she was really close to.
What are the rules?!
Now that's more like it!
The deadline is
sunset tomorrow.
Whoever finds out
her weakness first, wins.
And I have the perfect prize
for the game's lucky winner.
We wanna play, too!
I guess that means
we're all competing.
Where'd you get
those pictures of Haruhi?!
Hey, wait a minute.
Where did you get
those pictures Kyo-chan?
I have my sources.
How about we just leave
it at that for the moment.
This is the place.
It's the most haunted
spot in all of Okinawa.
The locals don't even
come out here.
They say that the only time
you can even find this cave
is at low tide.
Evidently, many people have
died down here from drowning.
And their souls still linger,
taking revenge on anyone
who happens to come inside.
Look!
What's going on? Are you
trying to freak me out?
What's wrong with you? I thought
everyone was afraid of ghosts.
But I've never seen
a real one.
Haru-chan! Would you
come over here?!
What the?
Are you sure it's okay to drive
a truck like this on the sand?
Well, we're ready whenever
you are, private police people,
please lower the door!
Yes Sir!
It's dark and scary in here!
I feel like I can't breathe!
What's wrong, Honey-senpai?
Mori, uh, you're my
senpai, not a sentai.
This game's harder
than I thought it'd be.
No joke. I'm totally
bored with it already.
What kind of heroine is she?
She's gotta be afraid
of something, right?
What's up, boss?
What are you doing?
I found some rat snakes!
Surely she'll freak out
when she sees these.
Anyone would think those
are creepy, so it isn't really
a weakness.
Hold on. I thought there weren't
any rat snakes in Okinawa.
Another side dish!
Look up here, Haruhi!
What's up?!
The breeze up here feels great!
It's dangerous be careful!
This feels so good.
Hey! There are
chicks up there, man!
Aren't we lucky!
You ladies wanna hang out
with a couple of locals?
No thanks. Please,
just leave us alone.
Aw c'mon. We just wanna
show you girls how to have
a good time.
This is a private beach. You
guys are not allowed to be here!
Private? Does that
mean we're alone?
Why don't you stop
bothering them?
Weren't you jerks listening?
You better just leave 'em alone.
Oh, Haruhi!
Why You little runt.
Those aren't rat snakes! Those
are poisonous habu snakes!
What do I do with them?!
Come on guys, help me out!
Tamaki!
It's Haruhi!
What're you gonna do now, loser?
Don't hurt him!
Now don't you try and act
all tough, you little sissy boy!
I got an idea, kid.
How'd you like to take a dip?
Haruhi!
Hope you can swim!
Haru-chan!
Boss!
Where'd they go?
We took their ID cards and
respectfully asked them
to leave. The girls all went
back to the hotel and I've
called a doctor, he should be
arriving here any minute now.
Thank you.
I'm fine, you guys.
I don't need a doctor.
What were you thinking?
You know you're not like
Honey-senpai. You're not
a martial arts master.
Why did you confront them?
What made you think
you would stand a chance?
You against two boys.
But it doesn't matter that
they're boys and I'm a girl.
I was there- I had
to do something.
I didn't have time to think-
That's no excuse, you idiot!
Don't forget you're a girl!
Look, I'm sorry you had
to come save me, senpai,
but I don't understand
why you're so mad at me
right now. I don't think
I did anything wrong!
You don't think so?
Fine. Whatever you say.
But I'm not speaking to
you until you can admit that
you were wrong!
Ta-da!
Here ya go!
Don't they look yummy?!
I apologize that there aren't
any maids around
to help you cook, senpai.
It's no big deal. We appreciate
you letting us stay here.
Hey,Takashi, will you
go get Haru-chan?
It's awfully gloomy
out there, huh?
It looks like it's gonna rain.
It's not just gloomy outside.
It's pretty gloomy right here
in the dining room as well-
just take a look at senpai.
Come on, quit moping, boss.
You shouldn't have
picked a fight with her
in the first place.
Haruhi, where'd you
get that dress?
From my dad, he must've
repacked my bags when I wasn't
looking. He's always
trying to get me to wear
this frilly stuff.
That's awesome!
Way to go, Dad!
You look so cute, Haru-chan!
Well, this is uncomfortable.
Yeah, kind of awkward.
Let's dig in, Haru-chan!
These are the crabs we caught!
I bet they're delicious!
Wow, these crabs.
Taste in-crab-ible!
Get it?
Don't you think you've
had enough? Give it a rest.
Excuse me? I thought that
you weren't speaking to me.
You trying to be cute?
Okay fine, I get it.
It seems you refuse to admit
that you were wrong. See if I
care, then- I'm going to bed...
Kyoya, would you show me
to my room, please?
No problem. Well,
excuse me, everyone.
Maybe, he's right, maybe
I do need to learn a way
to protect myself.
Why did you confront them?
What made you think
you would stand a chance?
You against two boys.
So that's it;
he got to you, huh?
Well, it wouldn't hurt you to
learn martial arts or something.
But it's not like we're going
to force you to learn it.
Besides, that's not
the real issue here.
To be honest, we were
all a little worried about
how recklessly you acted.
What do you mean? I didn't
cause you guys any trouble
or anything.
That's not true, Haru-chan.
I think you should
apologize, okay?
You made us all worry.
Especially Tama-chan.
I think you need to
apologize to him the most.
So you, were worried
about me, but why?
You're hopeless.
You think?
Guys, I'm really sorry.
Aw, apology accepted
you little mutt!
You're so cute. We forgive you!
Is something wrong?
I'm not feeling so good.
You must've eaten too much crab.
Be strong, Haru-chan!
Let's get her to the
nearest restroom! Hurry!
Well, that was a waste
of a good meal.
I was in such a hurry,
I ran into the closest room
I could find. Where am I?
Are you okay?
I apologize, sir,
I didn't mean to intrude.
Don't be silly. It's just me.
Kyoya-senpai.
Senpai, I'm sorry. I really
didn't mean to make everybody
worry about me today.
Thanks, but I wasn't
especially worried.
Although, I did
have a hard time
separating Kaoru and Hikaru
from those two punks.
They almost beat them
half to death.
And because of you, I had to
send each of the girls a bouquet
of flowers to apologize.
They've been looking forward
to this trip and we don't
want to disappoint them.
I'll pay you back
for the flowers, senpai.
Each bouquet cost 50,000.
That's a grand total
of 600,000 yen, Haruhi.
Why did you turn the lights off?
If you want to, you could
pay me back with your body.
Surely, you aren't so naive
that you actually believe
a person's sex doesn't matter.
You've left yourself completely
defenseless against me.
So that's it.
You won't do it, Kyoya-senpai.
I know.
Because it wouldn't do you
any good. You wouldn't gain
anything from it.
You're right.
You're a fascinating
young woman, Haruhi.
But I've learned
something from this.
I guess I never realized,
what a nice guy you are, senpai.
I know what you're doing;
you're just trying to prove
what Tamaki said earlier.
Well think about it,
you idiot! You are a girl!
I know that you're
trying to prove his point.
You're just posing
as the bad guy.
Kyoya?
Do you have any lotion?
This sunburn is worse than I-
You bastard!
Here. Use as much
as you want, you big goof.
Nothing to be
gained from it, huh?
An interesting thought,
in its own way.
What were you doing
alone with him?
Nothing, really.
You expect me to believe
that nothing was going on?!
You were alone in his bedroom!
And why were the lights out?!
Don't you lie to me!
Never mind. You've
been through a lot today;
I'm sure you're tired.
You should get some sleep.
Senpai.
What's wrong, Haruhi?
It's nothing!
I just remembered there's some
business I have to take care of.
What business could you
have in a wardrobe?!
Haruhi, are you afraid
of thunder and lightning?
Why'd you lock
yourself in there?
It seems like it'd be
scarier locked up like that.
I'm all right. I'm used to
getting through stuff like this
by myself.
By yourself.
You're always by yourself,
all alone in your home.
You never call us for help
even though we're so close.
I get it.
I understand now, Haruhi.
I'm sorry I acted
the way I did.
You grew up without
relying on anyone else.
But not anymore.
You can come out now.
You don't have to be afraid.
I'll always be here
for you, Haruhi.
I promise that
you'll never be alone again.
Are you sure it's a good idea-
To leave the two of them alone?
She's with our Prince, Tamaki.
What could possibly go wrong?
Hey, Boss? We're coming in.
With the blindfold on you
can't see anything and then
the earplugs help
muffle any sound!
Wow, yeah, you're right!
You nasty pervert.
What kind of foreplay is that?!
It's not like that!
It's not what you think!
You'd better watch
your back, Haruhi.
I never would've pegged
the boss as an S&amp;M pervert.
I told you- it wasn't
like that at all!
I see. Well, now
I know what S&amp;M is.
I can't believe I almost
let you get away with it.
I wasn't doing anything freaky;
I was trying to help you!
Let's go.
Hey! Don't leave
without me! Wait you guys!
I never noticed! Haruhi is
perfectly suited to attend
an elite all-girls' school!
And that's exactly why
I can't let her transfer!
Next time, "A Challenge from
Lobelia Girl's Academy!"
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!