Mr. President.
Our circulation has
dropped into single digits.
Just give me
the numbers, please.
How many newspapers
did we sell this week?
Two copies.
That's all?
Yes, sir.
Ukyo, did you buy
a newspaper?
I did, sir.
And Sakyo, what about you?
Of course.
So you're saying
no one outside of
the newspaper club bought one?
Well, yes. Unfortunately, that
does seem to be the case, sir.
This is quite a predicament.
Next week's edition will be our
last paper of the 1st semester.
If we don't come up with
better results before
summer vacation,
the club will be shut down
before the end of
the school year.
Oh, by the way,
how's that other club doing?
Well, sir.
The Host Club's photo
collection, "I Love, Love, Love
Tamaki Special", sold out
as soon as it went on sale-
all 1,000 copies!
"Moe- Moe Ouran Diaries Vol.
8", the doujinshi put together
and published by Renge
Houshakuji, also sold out
as soon as it went on sale. It's
already in its second printing.
I should have known.
They're the ones who have the
most power here at Ouran.
Welcome back, Ladies.
Covering the Famous Host Club
But we can't do this, Tamaki.
There are so many
girls who love you,
and if we get any closer,
I'm afraid that they're
all going to hate me for it.
Princess. These beautiful
hydrangeas will keep us hidden
from the others.
You don't need to worry.
For this moment, I belong
to no one but you. My love,
the spirits of the hydrangeas
will keep our rendezvous
a secret.
Oh, Tamaki! I yearn
to be with you!
Princess!
Oh, my!
Sorry, Kaoru!
No way! I lost again?
Now go easy on him, princesses.
Kaoru is quite the crybaby.
Hikaru! That's not true!
I am not a cry-
So you're gonna deny it, huh?
What about when
the two of us are alone
playing punishment games?
Tell us what
happens then, Kaoru.
But, that's because, you-
Then what happens?! Tell me!
I really wanna know!
Wow, I've never noticed
that the courtyard
had such a lovely stream.
It's called a yarimizu channel.
It is said that during
the Heian era, people
would better experience
the seasons by watching the
petals or autumn leaves
that drifted along the water.
I had it specially made for all
of you hoping it would express
my desire to spend all
four seasons with you.
So then, what do you say,
ladies? This fall there's an
autumn leaves tea party
with a limited
number of invitations.
Sign me up!
Now watch as we
work together to eat soba
Oh, he's so cute!
It's so peaceful. Guess I'm
finally getting used to this.
Took me long enough,
it's been this way since
I started school here.
Haruhi! Duck!
Hikaru! You came this close
to snuffing out the light
of Haruhi's life!
So much for it
being peaceful...
Hey! It's your fault for
not catching the ball
in the first place, Boss.
Yeah- Who knew that
he'd be so bad at kemari.
So much for him being the
"Genji of Ouran Academy."
What?!
If we want the Newspaper Club
to survive, I'm afraid
we're going to have
to ask them for help.
No, Mr. President!
It's too dangerous
to get involved
with those guys!
He's right! Not only would
the club get shut down
but you could be expelled!
You think so? Well, check
this out! Starlight Kick!
What?!
So fast!
Take care of yourself!
Calm down, there's
nothing to worry about.
We have no choice but
to ask them for help.
However that doesn't mean
I'll fall victim to their-
President!
Really. We're terribly
sorry about that.
Don't worry- it's no big deal.
Could've happened
to anyone, right?
Just a ball flying through
a window and hitting me
upside the head-
Please accept our apology!
Well, this works out perfectly.
I was just thinking about
approaching the Host Club
about a cover story.
I don't suppose you'd
be interested?
I didn't know we had
a Newspaper Club.
It's more gossip rag
than newspaper.
Yeah, like a trashy tabloid.
It's filled with stories about
scandalous love affairs,
family power struggles,
and junk like that.
It's just a lame gossip
rag that specializes
in stirring up scandal.
And everyone knows
it's all lies,
so nobody reads it anymore.
You know, I guess we have kind
of lost sight of the truth
because we've been so
worried about drawing in
more readers.
It's a shame we're just now
realizing our error, now that
the paper is at risk.
We've finally realized what
we should have been reporting
to the students of Ouran.
Help us, please.
For our last paper of this
semester we'd like to
do an up-close special edition,
revealing the charms of
Ouran's Host Club members.
I'm begging you, without your
help, our club will close.
You can count on us. On behalf
of the Host Club I accept-
We have to decline.
But Kyoya! He got
hurt because of me!
What's the big deal, huh?
Sorry, we have a policy
prohibiting us from sharing
personal information with
anyone other than our guests.
But we'd be more than happy
to pay any medical expenses
related to your injury.
And another thing, what makes
you think that we'd want
to help you spread more
rumors and gossip?
We've got a reputation
to uphold and you'd
just ruin it.
Besides, you guys cause a lot
of trouble for other people.
And who'd wanna get
mixed up with that?
It's scary how much they don't
realize about themselves.
I understand. Well, I guess
you really can't erase
the sins of the past, can you?
People won't even give you
the opportunity to try
and redeem yourself.
My head is killing me!
President!
I'm okay. Don't worry, you two.
Oh no- I'm getting dizzy again!
President!
No, wait, I'm fine!
I guess all we can do at this
point is disband with grace.
No, you don't have to!
You can always
make a fresh start.
We'll help. We will rally
the power of our Host Club,
and we can reestablish the
Newspaper Club together!
Well, count us out.
You're way too trusting,
boss. We can't just go along
with everything you do forever.
Yeah, we've had enough.
We're leaving too,
Tamaki. We're holding an
evaluation meeting,
mostly about you.
Hold it!
How can you be so
heartless? These men are
about to lose their club.
Don't you feel sorry for them?!
Their family's breaking up!
As your president,
I demand you help them!
And that is a direct order!
We're not going to do it.
Well, he's obviously
upset with us.
Yeah, he hasn't even
changed clothes.
I hate it when he
ignores us when
we're right in from of him.
He's such a child.
Nah, Tama-chan's just
a lonely guy, you know?
A club is like a family.
Their 'family's' about to be
broken up.
I feel sorry for them.
I hate to give in but would it
really be that bad to help out
with their newspaper?
What?
Hey, since when are you
taking his side?
Since never. Just listen okay?
I know any moment now he's
gonna look over here
with those puppy-dog eyes
he uses when
he wants something
and none of us will
be able to say no
and so he'll win.
Let me guess, you're speaking
from experience, aren't you?
Besides, maybe I'm wrong, but
isn't this the kinda thing
you guys usually go for?
Well, no. This seems like
more trouble than its worth.
What about you
Honey-senpai?
Count me out. I have this
cake to eat, and Takashi
sticks with me, right?
Those are the eyes.
Puppy-dog eyes.
There will be some conditions.
The outline for their article
will be submitted by us.
Interviews are
strictly prohibited.
And it is vital that
our client's identities
be kept confidential.
Do we agree?
Well, if you think its
cool, Kyoya-senpai.
Then we do too.
I'll do it since
Kyo-chan says it's okay.
That's the
shadow-king for you.
Of course! If you'll
allow us to cover you,
we promise to observe
your conditions.
Well then, you may
start tomorrow.
Excellent!
So how is that bump on
your forehead feeling?
Oh, that, it's no big deal-
I hardly feel it anymore.
I owe a lot to this bump
because without it,
we'd never have come
together for this article.
That's true, but we're still
very sorry it happened.
I brought you a little something
as an apology of sorts.
This is a first-aid kit, made
by my family's company.
Thank you- I appreciate it.
No problem. Please excuse me.
Oh, it just dawned on me.
Your family runs
the Otori Group, right?
they manufacture medical
equipment, don't they?
We mostly deal with
hospital management.
I'm so glad that we'll
be working together.
My father's a
president as well,
of the Komatsuzawa
Publishing firm.
Yes, I am well aware of that.
So being president of the
Newspaper Club is your way
of preparing to take over
the family company?
Well yes, to an extent, but
I have this younger brother;
he's a bright young man and my
father's very proud of him,
you see.
So now my father's decided
to turn future management
of the company over to
my younger brother.
And thereby passing over me.
The eldest son, first born.
However, if I'm able to finish
my third year at Ouran Academy
as the president of a
successful Newspaper Club,
I think he may reconsider my
candidacy as his successor.
Do you understand? I cannot
allow this club to fall apart-
no matter what.
Please excuse me.
Mr. President, are we to
assume you were trying
to win over Kyoya Otori?
But of course. My only real
enemy here is Tamaki Suou.
Originally I had planned to
use the power of the
school newspaper to become
popular here at Ouran Academy.
But then Suou showed up and
started his stupid Host Club
and suddenly he became the
big man on campus.
But President, that's not
what Sakyo and I heard.
Yeah, I thought the
newspaper you printed before
was just as unpopular
as it is now.
That's enough!
It only takes one call to
Mother and I can have
all business between
our publishing firm
and your families cut off.
They've obviously
got special standing.
They're not affiliated with
any sports or cultural clubs.
They don't even
have an advisor!
All they do in that club
is fake romance.
Those poor girls who visit
them are being suckered.
It must be Suou's way
of flaunting his power.
Using his parents' authority
to let he and his buddies
do whatever they want
with those girls.
All of those Host Club members,
including Kyoya Otori,
were supposed to be
my underlings!
Tamaki Suou, he's more
shrewd than you'd expect.
He may seem like a friendly
guy- he's got the act down.
But I'm positive he's
got a dark side.
I'll dig until I find
something scandalous.
That'll teach him a lesson.
The Daruma doll fell over!
The Daruma doll fell ov-er!
I saw you move
Hikaru and Kaoru!
President, what on earth
are we witnessing?
Could it be some kind
of new religion?
Why're you asking me? How
the hell should I know?
You know, I can't blame you
for being shocked.
I was unfamiliar with it myself,
but it's a commoner's game.
They have a wide variety
and none of them require
spending any money, all you
need is a few friends
to play with.
And what does this have to
do with our coverage
of the Host Club?
You need to learn friendliness!
If you want to clear the
negative reputation of
the Newspaper Club and
attempt to capture the hearts
of your readers, you must try
to be more down to earth!
I can just imagine the
headlines now.
"The Handsome Boys of the Host
Club Enjoy Commoners' Games!"
With pictures of us frolicking
in the scenery of early summer-
it would be the perfect
facelilft for your frontpage!
And it gives you the chance
to show that a certain
commoner is happier now
-reliving his childhood
here with us!
Great, he's looking at me.
I should probably start acting
like I'm happy to be here.
But President. I don't think I
understand what he's saying.
Are you sure that this guy
isn't just a complete idiot?
Do not let your guard down
just yet. This is all
part of his strategy.
The commoner
in question, perfect.
Why can't this be over?
You're Fujioka, right?
You wouldn't mind if I asked
you a few questions, would you?
Um, sure.
So why did you
join the Host Club?
Well, uh. Honestly, I joined
'cause I was forced to.
You're an honor student on
a scholarship, correct?
Uh-huh,
that's right.
So in other words, the
fact that you're a member
of this club is just another
example of how the Suou family
loves to flaunt their power.
Say what?
Now if you would,
please tell me all
about Tamaki's dark side...
If you can help me out here
I just might be able
to set you free.
Sorry but as far as I can tell
he doesn't have a dark side.
That can't be right. You
expect me to believe that
a group of high schoolers
actually enjoys
playing these
childish games?
I don't think it's that weird.
You've got to be kidding me!
Chop!
Now come and get us!
Hey wait! That's not where
you're supposed to cut,
you know!
Next we're
playing kankeri!
And you're "it", okay Kyoya?
If I must.
Starlight kick!!
If you honestly think I'm going
fall for the same trick again,
you've got another
thing com-
President!
Haruhi, come with me! Run!
I don't think he has a
dark side. Could he?
Now that I think about it,
I don't know anything
about Tamaki-senpai's family.
One. Two--
Damn it. I refuse to put up with
his shenanigans any longer.
Four. Five.
You'll pay for this,
Tamaki Suou.
Six.
Did you get us lost, senpai?
We are lost, aren't we?
Look, Haruhi! I found a great
hiding place over here!
Yeah, we're totally lost.
So we're stranded til
someone finds us?
Great; it's a good thing
you made Kyoya-senpai "it".
Are you messing with me?
You know, I never thought I'd
be playing these silly games
again once I got
into high school.
But don't you think
this is fun?
I guess. But I haven't played
any of this stuff since I was
an elementary student.
Yeah? I see.
It's new to me. When I was
growing up I never really had
any friends that were my age.
My mother would get sick
very easily. I was always
worried about her so I didn't
go out and play much.
Instead I would do my best
to cheer her up.
I'd always sit beside her
and play the piano.
That's probably why now I love
playing these silly games
with all of you.
It's a lot of fun!
We should do this
again sometime.
I think so, too.
I'm writing the article!
But wait, Mr. President!
It's too dangerous to
write gossip about Suou!
You don't have any
evidence, sir!
Who needs evidence? All I
have to do is expose him
and everyone will see it! If
I set my mind to it,
I can imagine any number of
articles that would cause
a commotion among the idiots
at this academy.
I'm going to expose Tamaki
for the twit he is.
Hmm.
So, we were right all along.
You two.
Well, I guess it was
pretty obvious.
The boss is the only one
who hasn't caught on yet.
He can be really dense when
it pertains to anything
about himself.
I should warn you,
if you threaten him
there will be consequences.
Are you ready to have the
Hitachins and every other
club members' family
as your enemy?
I knew it! You're nothing
but lackies!
Tamaki's holding his parents'
power over all of you-
That's not true.
We don't hang out with
Tama-chan because of
his parents.
We love him. We all like
being around him and
that's why we
choose to be here.
He may be a hopeless idiot but-
Even so.
Kyoya. Let's start
a club together!
Why, hello there.
Haninozuka-senpai.
I know this is sudden but I
was wondering if you'd join
a new club
I'm starting?
Morinozuka-senpai!
You kids seem to have a lot
of free time.
If you ever get bored, you
should come join our new club!
Well?
What will you do?
Please leave Tama-chan
alone, okay?
I'll get you all! It's not
just about him anymore.
I'll write an article
that'll ruin all of you!
Go ahead, be my guest.
Although.
What do you think we should
do about this little disk?
You see, it's been here
since yesterday.
And it recorded everything.
President!
Just give
up already!
Let me explain it to you in
terms you can understand.
You would do well to remember
that the Otori Group
and the Hitachiin family
alone own enough stock
to remove your father
from his position
as president of the
Komatsuzawa Publishing Firm.
However. We would never
do something like that-
we are not like you.
What we strive for is
fundamentally different.
I found you!
Where's the
Newspaper Club?
They had to cancel.
Something came up.
They said they're
going to focus
on writing
respectable articles.
So maybe they'll get by
without having to shut down.
Oh, really?
That's good news.
Let's hurry back to the club
room and eat some cake!
Yeah.
That does sound good!
Cake! Cake!
Kyoya-senpai,
I was wondering.
Is the Suou family really
that big a deal around here?
Well. The foundation
of their business lies
in corporate finance,
but they do have some
extensive real estate as
well. You've heard of
The Roy Grand Hotel and the
Outo Theatre.
They also have a hand in
other things,
like school management
for example.
I didn't know that.
Which school?
Why, Ouran Academy.
You've been here long enough
that you should at least
know what the chairman of
the school board's name is.
You know,
if you think about it.
You're able to attend
school here because of
the financial aid you receive
from Tamaki's family.
You should be grateful to them.
Haruhi!
Hurry it up or we're going
to leave you!
I would hate for you to end
up lost again!
What happened? Haruhi's
gone missing?!
No, I just got a summer job
in Karuizawa.
Then my refreshing self
will come visit you!
Next time, "The Refreshing
Battle in Karuizawa".
The Ouran Host Club will
be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!