Haruhi Fujioka?
Hey, Arai.
So, uh, these
your friends?
Oh, yeah, this
is Hikaru and Kaoru-
they're in my class.
And this is-
-my sen-
While you act as my apprentice,
you can't treat me as Senpai.
An acquaintance of mine.
Misuzu.
Please don't add
any sound effects
to my moment of despair.
"Operation Haruhi
&amp; Hikaru's First Date"
I haven't seen
you since graduation.
Yeah- you cut all your hair
off. That's such a shame.
I don't think so. I
mean, since I cut it,
it has been easier to manage.
So how's Ouran treating you?
Do you keep in touch
with anyone from middle
school anymore?
Yeah. A little. Kazumi still
calls me. What about you?
So, then he's
a friend of Haruhi's
from middle school, huh?
They've had zero contact since
graduation so in my opinion-
they're not friends,
just former classmates.
So these guys are all in
a club with you?
Host Club.
Oh. Is that so?
Hey, Haruhi! Don't you think
you should be working?
You shouldn't be slacking off!
Misuzu said
I could take a break!
Hey, quit making more garbage
I'll have to take out.
It's not garbage.
I'm making a hamster home.
But senpai,
you don't have a hamster.
I'm not your senpai. I'm just
an acquaintance of yours.
Wow, who knew you Ouran
guys were so funny?!
You know, it's such
a prestigious school.
I've always imagined it was
a whole different world.
It's a different
world, alright.
To be honest with you Fujioka.
I was kinda worried
that you were gonna have
a hard time going to such
an elite school.
I'm glad to see
you're doing well.
Um, I mean. It's not like
I was the only one who was
worried about you,
lots of people were.
What's with him? He's
trying to use the refreshing
innocence approach.
Someone should tell him we
already had a
refreshment contest.
You're being
unusually critical.
I'm just sayin'.
It's obvious this guy
has a thing for Haruhi.
It's sickening to watch
him try and flirt.
Hikaru! What's wrong with you?!
Quit acting like such a jerk!
Hey, it's no big deal.
He's right; I did have
a thing for you once.
But who cares, you already
turned me down, right?
Why do you look
so surprised?
Well, I didn't know.
You have to fill us in
on this story, Arai.
Now When did this happen?
Well, it was about a year ago.
There she is! Fujioka!
I heard you're taking the honor
student exam for Ouran Academy.
You are? Well, you just might
make it in with your grades.
Although. I was sure you'd
be going to Higashi High.
I'm taking the test for
Higashi, too. I don't know if
I'll be accepted to Ouran.
Yeah. Well, I guess I'll just
cheer for you. I'd have liked
to go to the same high school
as you, though.
Well, okay, then. You really
should have said something
to me sooner.
You mean?
I'm pretty sure Ouran has
more than one honor student
scholarship to award.
Oh, that...
And even if there is only one,
you can't give up on going to
the school of your dreams
for someone else's sake.
If only one of us gets in, there
won't be any hard feelings,
right? We should
both do our best.
I know!
Let's go and ask
the counselor about it.
Fujioka!
I- I want. I want
you to go with me!
Yeah.
I wanted check the
application deadline, too.
Let's go to the
staff room together.
Haruhi.
You broke this innocent man's
heart just to get a laugh
from some sick joke?
No, that's not what happened-
This crime's pretty
serious, huh?
I'm so sorry.
So you're turning me down
again a whole year later?!
Don't worry, Fujioka!
I'm over it already!
You didn't realize what
I meant so that means
you weren't interested.
But you know, I was always
drawn to that faraway look
in your eyes.
And the way you would
look someone in the eyes
when you spoke to them.
I liked that about you, I always
thought you were special.
You think that much of my
little girl? Don't worry;
I'll never forget
your gallantry!
Wow. You guys went to Kyoto
for your middle school
field trip? How unusual that
you stayed in the country.
Nah, it's quite normal
for us, really.
Well, I've always
been a fan of Kyoto.
I can't tell you how many times
I've had to tour the temples
with him.
What should we do Hikaru?
They're having a good time
over there-
we could join them.
No. I'm not going to.
I can't believe the boss
is actually hanging out
with that jerk.
Hikaru! Kaoru!
Get over here! This may be
our only chance to hear
what Haruhi was like
in middle school!
Sorry, but I'm not interested!
Man, how stupid can you
guys get? Where's the fun
in sitting around talking
about somebody's past?
I don't see the appeal.
Besides, doesn't that guy
realize Haruhi doesn't
want anything to do with him?
She's got plenty of friends.
So she doesn't need
you around, get it?
That's not something
for you to decide, Hikaru!
I'm not gonna tolerate
you insulting my friends
anymore! You got that?
But why- why should anyone
else even matter to you?
I thought we were your
friends! Are we or aren't we?!
Hikaru! Wait for me!
Their world is still
so small. It's such a shame.
That's some temper
you've got there.
Aren't you a bit old for that?
Don't pretend like you
weren't upset, too.
Well, maybe I was, but I'm
more rational than you.
I don't think I've seen you
act so selfishly before,
like a little child.
Haruhi was surprised.
Well, I couldn't help it.
I was really upset
but I can't figure out why.
Here's an idea; why don't you
go apologize to Arai?
I'm sorry about that, Arai.
It's okay. I don't know what
I did, but whatever it was
it sure seemed
to set him off, huh?
Hika-chan.
I was outta line.
I'm sorry.
Thanks, don't worry about it.
Well, see you soon, Fujioka.
Bye, guys!
Bye bye!
So, Kaoru, tell me why you're
pretending to be Hikaru.
Hey! What happened to that
scratch on your cheek?
I just covered it up with
some concealer!
I don't think Hikaru's
temper is going to let up
anytime soon.
He's no fun when he's like
this, so I've got a small favor
to ask of you.
How would you like to go out
with me tomorrow on a date?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hold on. Where's Kaoru?
Well, uh.
I was gonna take Haruhi
out to make up for what
happened yesterday, but I
seem to have caught a cold.
You're not feeling too good?
Will you take her
out in my place?
She's expecting me to hang out
with her all day so make sure
you show her a good time.
And it better go well or she's
never gonna talk to you again!
Think you can you handle it?
Yeah, that shouldn't
be a problem.
Are you sure?
Hey, come on.
You think I can't do it?
Well, you've never really
gone out with anyone before.
So just listen carefully, 'k?
You have to tell other
people how you feel
or they'll never know.
And remember.
What were you thinking, Kaoru?
What should do we do?
Wanna go home?
No, I told him I'd hang
out with you today
so we might as well,
but what's up with that outfit?
Is it weird?
Kinda.
Haruhi!
Be careful,
boss they'll see us!
Why did Hikaru and Haruhi
end up on a date anyway?!
I don't understand!
How are yesterday's events
even related to this?!
You know, this might be
Haru-chan's first date.
You're going to pay for that!
And look at what she's wearing!
It's cute! Super cute!!
Oh, I can explain.
Good morning, Miss Fujioka.
Time to get ready.
Hey! What are you doing?!
No fair! No fair! No fair!
I dunno, boss.
It's hard for you to understand
but it would be good
for Hikaru find other people
he can feel close to.
The only people
we've ever been able
to depend on are ourselves.
We didn't care what anyone
else thought about us.
That's probably how we ended
up so self-centered.
So you're admitting it?
I guess you could say Hikaru's
immature, he lets his emotions
take over. See, I'm not
sure he's even aware of it.
But I can tell that
he cares about Haruhi.
He just doesn't know how to
react so his emotions run wild.
He's selfish and wants
all of her attention.
Are we or aren't we?!
He wants to be acknowledged
by her but doesn't know
how to make that happen.
If you want true friends,
friends who aren't only
your toys, you have to learn
to respect them. That's the
only way you can have a
meaningful relationship.
And I think it's about
time that Hikaru learned
that lesson himself.
Kaoru, that was amazing.
So in other words,
this date is basically a test
to see if Hikaru can
handle being thoughtful
towards others, right?
Just promise me you won't
interfere with them, okay?
Fine but then why are you
making us follow them?
Because, there's no reason
we should miss out on
watching something
this interesting.
So, where do you
want to go, Haruhi?
Kaoru said he'd plan everything.
So I didn't really give it
much thought. Any ideas?
Well, there's not anything
that I need to do here.
Be sure you show her
a good time!
I know... why don't we
go to that outlet mall
by the train station? They've
got cheap clothes there.
That's cool but do you need
to buy some clothes?
No, there's no way I'd buy
my clothes at that place.
Then let's skip it.
What a pain.
Everything looks fine now, but
Misuzu said it might rain.
I sure hope there aren't
any thunderstorms today.
I never knew you were
so into the weather.
How can he call himself
a Host Club member?!
This is the lamest excuse
for a date I've ever seen!
Look at him! I should
switch with Hikaru!
I'll show her a good time!
That would ruin everything!
Get out there Kyoya! Act
like a punk and pick a fight
with Haruhi so Hikaru
will have to rescue her!
Where do you dream
this stuff up?
Ice cream! Ice cream! Does
anyone want ice cream?!
Bad idea.
That was creepy; that old guy
kinda looked like Honey-senpai.
One ice cream, please.
Hey, you shouldn't run off
like that, Haruhi!
I heard this place is famous
for their ice cream.
Here. I'll let you
have the first taste.
If it sucks then
we're playing a penalty game.
What a pretty young lady!
Here's another one for you,
on the house.
Thank you, sir.
Delicious!
You're right.
It is pretty good.
What do you think
you're doing?!
It was finally going
well, you idiot!
You think I'm gonna let them
share an ice cream cone
like a couple?!
That's indirect kissing!
According to this,
they're pickled yams.
That's pretty weird, huh?
C'mon, pickled food is so lame.
Who'd want to eat that crap?
Try it.
It's not that bad.
I'll take two bags
of these, please.
You're not supposed
to buy souvenirs until
the last day of your trip.
You're gonna be in Karuizawa
for a while, right?
These are a gift.
I'm getting them for Kaoru.
Hey, listen, do you think
the others would be up for
souvenir shopping tonight?
We could always come back
to these shops later and pick
out a few more gifts for Kaoru.
I don't understand.
How can you tell
that I'm upset about Kaoru?
I just can.
Well, let's go.
We take our eyes off of them
for a second and suddenly
everything's great!
That's true but I get
the feeling Haruhi's
the one in charge here.
It looks like the
ice cream stand helped
smooth things over.
I doubt it.
We should get going,
if we get caught.
It's gonna ruin everything.
And anyway, I don't think
the boss can handle
much more of this.
It looks like
so much fun. Lucky.
Did you just
hear something?
What? No, I didn't hear
anything; it does look like
it's going to rain, though.
Think we should head back?
Probably.
Then, let's head to the
street and, hail a cab, okay?
Is that you, Fujioka?
What are you up to?
Hey Arai, what are
you doing here?
Well, this is my uncle's store.
You guys out doing
some shopping?
Yeah but we were
just about to leave.
Yeah? We've got a car
that can take you back.
Let me just ask my uncle
I don't wanna be
a bother...
It's no problem.
I wouldn't want you
to get caught in the rain.
Don't worry about it,
we're getting a taxi.
C'mon, don't waste
your money on a taxi.
Hey, we should
accept his offer.
The sooner we get home,
the better.
Well, I guess you'll be
riding home alone, then.
Hikaru.
Just do whatever
you want, okay?
You guys can catch
up and reminisce
but leave me out of it!
Wait!
Not again. Why's he so
upset about you hanging out
with an old friend?
I mean, surely he's got
some of his own, right?
The two of us have been
together since we were born,
so we haven't ever needed
any other friends.
Check out that lightning!
I sure hope those two didn't
get stuck in the rain.
Tamaki dear, please
try to settle down.
I should go
look for them, huh?
Hello? This is Pension Misuzu.
Oh, it's you Arai. What is it?
What? Haruhi and Hikaru?
Thank you. Hikaru should
have his cell with him
so I'll try giving him
a call. G'bye now.
Evidently Hikaru left Haduhi
in front of the produce shop
and decided he would head
back on his own.
Arai said Haduhi took off
after Hikaru and that's when
it started pouring. He
was worried so he called
to make sure they
made it home okay.
Hey, what's up boss? You've got
great timing- think you can
send a cab to get me? I haven't
had any luck hailing one.
You idiot! I want you to turn
around and start looking
for Haruhi, right now!
What kind of jerk would leave
a girl out in a thunderstorm
like this by herself?!
Now you listen to me,
Haruhi is terrified of thunder!
Whenever she hears it,
she gets so scared she
can't even move!
Why don't you spend less
time concentrating on
your jealousy and worry
about someone else for once!
What does he mean by that?
How the hell was I
supposed to know,
if she never told me?
I sure hope there aren't
any thunderstorms today.
Did you just hear something?
Hey, we should
accept his offer.
The sooner we get
home the better.
There's no way I could've
figured that out!
Haruhi? Hey,
are you in here?
Haruhi?
You have to tell other people
how you feel or they'll
never know. Remember.
Whenever you care a lot
for someone, Hikaru.
It's important you pay
attention to any subtle
little hints they drop.
I don't understand.
How can you tell that
I'm upset about Kaoru?
I just can.
Haruhi.
Hika-
Sorry.
I'm sorry for running off
and leaving you.
And for the things I said about
your friend Arai, I'm so sorry.
Thanks, Hikaru. I forgive you.
I'm sorry.
What's up?
Hey! Good morning, Arai!
I brought you a watermelon. My
uncle's got the best in town!
Oh Wow! It's huge!
It's certainly
an impressive melon.
Here.
Thanks a lot.
By the way. A question
about your strategy
did you ever consider the
possibility the date might go
too well and those two
might fall in love?
Nah, it's still
too soon for that.
Hikaru's kind of a dummy.
Hey! Come down here!
It's time for some melon!
Well. Then he's lucky because
our club's full of dummies.
What's going on
Kyoya-senpai? You never talk
during the preview.
Well, I make it a rule
not to do anything if
there's nothing in it for me.
Next time, "Kyoya's
Reluctant Day Off"!
The Ouran Host Club
will be waiting for you!
We'll see you then!