Haruhi?
You sure you don't
want any breakfast?
No thanks.
Well, I'm off then.
Welcome, miss.
I know you.You're one of
the Ootori family's sons,
aren't you?
Unfortunately, you're the
third son so you can never
be the family's successor.
What can I do for you
today, madamoiselle?
You can tell me how much
Haruhi Fujioka is still
in debt with the Host Club.
Haruhi?
Someone to see you.
How are you today?
I couldn't help but notice
that my Tamaki seemed
to have a soft spot for you.
Just what are you getting
at? Are you saying you're
jealous of me?
Oh listen to you!
Tamaki won't be coming today.
I warned him I would be
upset if he ever showed
his face at the Host Club again.
I wonder what
happened to Tama-chan?
I'm getting worried,
something's up with him
after what he said yesterday.
As of today, Lady Éclair
Tonnerre and I are officially
engaged. Furthermore,
the Host Club will be
permanently dissolved--
after the Ouran Fair.
Alright gentlemen,
no more idle chatter.
Our guests are waiting for us.
Senpai, it's like
you don't even care.
It's our job to take care
of our guests to the best
of our abilities. Remember,
They're looking to all of us
to entertain them.
Their happiness is
of utmost importance.
He's right, Kao-chan!
Honey-senpai,
What're you doing?!
C'mon, Hikaru.
Let go Mori-senpai!
Thank you for all
of your hard work, Haruhi.
After that request
from Lady Éclair.
Your debt has been paid.
Now you've finally repaid us
for that Renaissance vase
you broke.
So, You're free to quit
the Host Club, if you want.
This is Our Ouran Fair.
When they're young many
assume they have all
the time in the world but
really that is never the case.
Don't waste your time
with something that will
ultimately have no value.
You don't know anything
about the Host Club.
Kyoya-senpai works around
the clock to make sure
that everyone here is
enjoying themselves.
And did you ever stop to think
that entertaining others
might give each
of us fulfillment?
How can you possibly say
that what we do here
is just a waste of our time?
And I don't care what you say
I think Kyoya-senpai
is amazing.
I see so that must be
the honor student Kyoya
told me about.
I'm concerned about our
standing with Grand Tonnerre.
They've recently been buying
up Japanese companies
right and left.
Don't worry, everything will
be fine. Once we finally have
an heir, the Suou family
will prosper once again.
After all, its not like the
boy can turn against us.
But, Tamaki has never been
interested in anything
involving the family. What have
you done to change his mind?
I told him that if he asked
Lady Éclair to marry him .
I would allow him
to see his mother.
But you can't be serious?
Your child is having to make
amends for the indiscretions
of your youth,
my dear son.
Tamaki won't be coming today.
I warned him I would be upset
if he ever showed his face
at the Host Club again.
Tell me, are you
Tamaki's lover?
No miss, not at all.
I see. That's good to hear.
Then I guess you must mean
nothing to him.
While I may not be his lover.
I know that I am
not nothing to him.
I think it's best you
not have any contact with
your friends for a while.
It'll make it harder
for you to leave.
Come in.
There is a visitor here
to see you, ma'am.
Please have them come in.
Mr. Otari, why are you here?
I should be asking you
the same question.
Don't you worry about him.
Sir, It's a pleasure
to see you again.
It's my fault that Kyoya
joined the Host Club.
I'm really sorry.
But sir. I don't understand
what you're doing here.
We're terribly sorry
we had to ask you to come
all this way. I hope the
trip hasn't burdened you.
No, on the contrary,
I'm always quite happy
to avoid the press.
From what I understand,
my medical equipment company
is about to be bought out from
under me by Grand Tonnerre.
And you know, it probably
serves Kyoya right.
The company I was
considering handing over
to him will forever
be out of his hands now.
Excuse me sir but
there's one more thing.
I've a favor to ask you.
Kyoya-senpai,
what's with this outfit?
We told you, it's a costume
for the special parade.
You look so cute Haru-chan!
I don't understand why
am I the only person
dressed as a girl?
Aw c'mon it's cosplay
so its okay for you
to dress like a girl.
I am one, you know.
Well?
No luck. He's not there.
I can't believe
senpai didn't show.
I really thought he was gonna
make it despite what she said.
Hello, Shima? Been a while,
hasn't it? It's Kyoya.
This is about
Master Tamaki, isn't it?
I'm sorry Kyo-ya
but the Master will be
departing for France soon.
I tried to talk him out of it
but he said the Suou family
had forgiven his beloved mother
and that he was finally
going to get to see her again.
He also said that if he stayed
at Ouran any longer.
his capriciousness would only
continue to make trouble
for you and everyone
else in the club,
How could he be so stupid?
Evidently Tamaki is planning
to return to France.
Tama-chan is going
to leave us?!
You kidding me?! We just can't
let it end so suddenly!
Hikaru.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes?
I was just thinking.
If the Master's mother really
is as remarkable
a woman as he claims
she is then I can only imagine
that she would be upset
with the manner in which the
Master has chosen to leave
Ouran Academy.
Do you know when
he's leaving, Shima?
I'm afraid his flight
is this evening.
Why's he leaving so soon?
He would have left sooner
but he said he had to wait
until the Oran Fair was ending.
Tamaki!
Tama-chan!
No way!
The Ouran Fair
isn't even over yet!
My family's car should be
in the parking lot!
Haruhi, Let's go!
We're in a hurry can
you drive us?
I'm sorry sir, but.
What is it? What's wrong?
Well you see, the thing is.
You want to tell me
your orders? Let me guess,
you were hired
to protect Lady Éclair.
I'm truly sorry it has come
to this but as you know,
as members of the
Ootori private police
we answer to your father.
Damn it!
I'm terribly sorry sir but
we've been ordered not
to allow any of you to
leave, even if we have
to stop you by force.
Hikaru, take the carriage.
If you use the back hills
bypass you can cut them off.
It's Haninozuka.
And Morinozuka!
C'mon!
Haruhi. Go get
that idiot. Hurry.
Now go! This is your chance!
Don't just stand there!
Stop that carriage!
Takashi. Don't go easy on 'em!
Don't worry, I won't.
I warned you guys! Picking on
my friends is a big no-no!
You should never underestimate
the Ouran Host Club.
Yeah.
Hikaru, Kaoru, Haruhi,
please bring him back.
Hikaru! Don't you think
we should slow down?
Somebody could get hurt!
We're not slowing down
'til we get the boss back!
But Hikaru.
If it wasn't for Tamaki
then the two of us
would still only be lost souls.
We were able to become
friends with Haruhi
and the others because the Host
Club brought us together.
To think that all of it could
end so suddenly like this--
--is something that
I can't tolerate!
No Hikaru! Hikaru! Hikaru!
Hikaru are you okay?
Is your arm hurting you?
This can't be the end, boss.
Its just not fair,
the Host Club's the only thing
that made us happy, damn it.
Hikaru.
Well, I'm off then.
What? You can't talk
to your dad about it?
What's the matter, Haruhi?
What do you mean?
I'm just not hungry
this morning, that's all.
You can't fool me,
kiddo. The last time
you skipped breakfast was
after your mom's funeral.
And it was a while before
you could eat again.
So, I won't get to see
mommy anymore?
There are many things
in this world that you
cannot ever change no matter
how desperately you try.
Just remember Haruhi
you have to stay brave,
even if it seems like
your world is crumbling
around you sometimes.
What's she doing?
What's the matter, Tamaki?
You haven't said
a word since we left.
You're a host, aren't you?
Come on, entertain me.
I have a question,
are you sure about this?
Will you even be happy married
to me or are you just,
following orders?
Haruhi?!
That's Haruhi Fujioka?
What are you doing,
Haruhi?! This is dangerous!
Stop that carriage now!
Senpai! Please come back
to Ouran!
I mean it! Stop the carriage!
All of us would be completely
lost without you, Senpai!
But they, they all said they
were put out by the Host Club.
You really are an idiot!
What's wrong with you?!
After all this time we've been
together you still can't tell
when we're joking and
when we're serious?!
Everyone loves being
in the Host Club!
We really do!
Even me, Senpai. I love being
part of the Host Club too!
Haruhi!
Senpai!
That was reckless, Haruhi.
You have to be more careful.
Look at you,
you're soaking wet.
A little water
never hurt anyone.
Besides, people are always
telling me that I'm dripping
with good looks.
Tama-chan! Haru-chan!
Hey Boss!
Oh man he's such a moron.
Let's go ahead.
Miss Éclair, you heard
the stories that housekeeper
tells back home, haven't you?
The one who's always talking
abut her son who loved to play
the piano for her.
Is he really as sweet
as you say he is?
Thanks Eclair.
I was going to give him
the opportunity to see
his mother again.
He's such a fool.
But even so, even for someone
like me, he still smiled.
I'm sorry that we
caused you concern.
It looks as though Grand
Tonnerre will not be purchasing
my company after all.
An unexpected backer turned
up they bought the company
before Tonnerre had a
chance and the backer said
that he was turning all the
management rights over to me.
That was a bold move.
Which funds manager was it?
A student investor,
called "K.O.".
He cleverly left his name out
of the deal but it didn't
take me long to figure
out who it was.
"K.O." is Kyoya Ootori the new
backer was none other than
my own son.
At least we know we don't have
to worry about the future.
I thought I knew how brilliant
Kyoya was but it seems
he's even smarter
than I thought.
Maybe so but I think your son is
the one who's truly amazing.
I am responsible for the
entirety of Kyoya's education.
I always knew that he would
surpass his older brothers
someday.
However, I must say I'm shocked.
While I can imagine Kyoya
taking over a company, I never
dreamed he'd turn around
and give it right back
to its original owner.
As Kyoya grew up I
was constantly dangling
the Ootori family companies
in front of his face,
torturing him with something
he could never have.
Now not only has he taken it
out from under me by force
but he's basically told me he
doesn't want it and has thrown
it back in my face.
Do you understand
what that means?
It means he's
finally found it.
He's found something that has
an even greater value to him.
And that's probably
thanks to Tamaki.
Though our companies sometimes
cause us to compete.
I think we'll get along
just fine from now on.
Agreed, I think we can
get along famously .
Just like our two sons do.
I almost forgot,
there was one thing that
I wanted to run by you.
That honor student girl,
Haruhi Fujioka, was it?
I think that she would make a
wonderful bride for my Kyoya
in the future. I just wanted
you to know my intentions.
Well unfortunately it looks like
we're not going to get along
after all I'm sorry but that's
one thing I could never allow,
my friend.
Only those with excellent
social standing and those from
filthy rich families are lucky
enough to spend their time here
at the elite,
private school Ouran Academy.
The Ouran Host Club is where
the school's handsomest boys,
with too much time on their
hands, entertain young ladies
who also have too much
time on their hands.
Think of it as Ouran Academy's
elegant playground for
the super-rich and beautiful.
Remember, you're to come and
visit us in Music Room #3
whenever you'd like.
The Ouran Host Club will be
waiting for you.
And we wanna thank you from
the bottom of our hearts.
We'll see you then!