At the stroke of midnight,
the carriage would
change back
into a pumpkin.
But this particular
spell wasn't cast
by a fairy godmother.
All right.
Next item on the agenda.
I move to discuss
what the class plans
will be for next week.
Next week?
Yeah, Halloween.
Oh Haruhi, you've only been
a student at Ouran Academy
since high school, right?
So you don't know.
After we've finished
taking our exams
for the fall, we're
allowed a few days off
until the end of October.
And we get to throw
costumes parties
on campus to celebrate.
And also, to promote
comraderie, each class
is allowed to use
an entire day for a special
class event of their choosing.
Event?
Right. They're
pretty fun actually.
Yeah, we socialize
or watch some old movies.
Stuff like that.
Boring! Boring! Boring!
Halloween.
The day that sounds the
death knell of summer and
ushers in the icy
breath of winter.
Halloween. Once a day when
ghouls walked the earth
and disguised
as ghouls we tried to
ward them all off.
Halloween. A day for
wearing costumes
and playing pranks
on trick-or-treaters
with reckless abandon.
Some people don't wait for
Halloween to dress up.
Some people cosplay year round.
I know that's right.
So, what's with the uniform?
Just between us, this is
the female uniform in
"Uki-doki Memorial 2,"
which isn't scheduled
for release until next spring.
What do you think?
I know important
people on the inside,
if you catch my drift.
Miss Hoshakuji,
we're having homeroom now.
Could you get down
off the desk please?
Tea parties and cosplay?
The Host Club does that
practically nonstop!
What our Halloween
requires is
something special!
Um, we're supposed
to decide this as a class.
So I propose holding
a Halloween Test-of-Courage
Tournament!
The bravest student wins!
A test-of-courage-
-tournament, you say?
Here's what we'll do.
We'll ask the superintendent
to give us access
to the school after hours,
when it's dark.
Then we'll all dress up
in our freakiest costumes
and proceed to have
the time of our lives
scaring the absolute crap
out of each other!
Yeah! We're in!
I really like the part about-
-it being dark.
That sounds awesome.
The school is
so spooky at night.
Oh, I'm getting so many
great ideas for this!
We can all take turns being
scared, and later get
our chance to scare
someone else!
Well now why don't we think
this through everyone.
We can't all
go individually.
We should be in teams
of at least three or four.
Yeah, teams would be scarier!
And anybody who leaves-
-gets featured on the front
page of the school newspaper
as "The Captain
of All Cowards."
Seconded!
Um. Alright then,
are there any objections
to the majority vote?
Are there any at all?
Is anyone
opposed to the idea?
Come on, anyone?
Oh very well.Then the
motion passes unanimously.
The class 1-A event for
this year will be a special
Halloween Test-of-Courage
Tournament.
"Until the Day
It Becomes a Pumpkin."
Trick or treat, girls. Give
me candy, or else your blood.
Halloween might be
a week away officially,
but here at the
Host Club, we start
haunting season
a little early.
Oh Tamaki, you make
such a handsome vampire.
Those fangs look real.
May I nibble your
lovely neck for a treat?
Oh no you mustn't.
You'll have to play
a trick on me instead.
And indeed I shall.
Oh, me next! Me next!
Me next! Me next! Me next!
Hello.
Why are you guys late?
Hurry up and change.
Sorry Boss. But from
now until Halloween-
-Count us out.
Okay?
What?
Count you out?
We're on the preparation
committee for a special event.
Class 1-A is sponsoring it.
Duty calls then.
Good luck without us
here for a week.
You have fun.
Hold on! Why is Haruhi going?
Well boss, she is
in our class you know.
Oh. The special event
is an after dark
Test-of-Courage
Tournament.
After dark?
I'm scared, Hikaru!
Hold me! Protect me!
I'm scared, Kaoru!
Haruhi. You're not going
to take part in this are you?
For decency's sake,
tell me you won't!
Calm down, Senpai.
It's just some harmless fun.
Harmless. She thinks it's--
--harmless?
Oh why me?
You won't go! You can't!
Daddy doesn't like it.
This is the magic spell.
We may just be members
of a host club--
--but the boss calls Haruhi
his daughter, and imagines
us to be members
of his family.
Okay, time to go now.
Boss, Adieu!
Wait! I could be
a valuable asset
to the planning committee!
Let me come too!
Nekozawa-senpai,
when did you--?
Well now,
isn't that interesting.
What was that? You think it
sounds like fun, Belzenef?
You may just be on to
something there.
If it's fear they want,
the Black Magic Club
will be happy to oblige.
After all what's Halloween
without a healthy dose of
pure unadulterated terror?
So, what kind of
budget-limit should
we put on costumes?
Once everyone starts
shopping,
they'll go all out.
Why don't we follow the
commoner's rule of keeping it
under 300 yen?
That should make
things interesting.
It would be a good idea
to have a doctor handy,
just in case anyone faints--
They all seem pretty
excited about this.
Okay, so under
three hundred yen,
needs a doctor present.
Hey, are we going to have food?
You have Nyctophobia?
So you're afraid of the dark?
Yes and you can add to
that horror-movie-phobia,
scary-ghost-story-phobia,
being-startled-by-
a-loud-noise-in-the-
other-room-phobia,
and
accidentally-seeing-trailers-for
horror-movies-phobia.
And what's with those
things? Why do they keep
showing them without
warning us about it first?
It just doesn't
make sense to me.
Whatever happened to civil
rights for the fraidy-cats
out there? Cowards are
people too! And what about
the other classes with their tea
parties? It's just so unfair!
Class Rep, calm down.
Oh my, I'm sorry.
If you were opposed to the
idea from the start,
why didn't you just bring
it up in the meeting?
I tried to. But I don't want
to look like I'm throwing
my weight around up there.
So I was counting on
your help to save me!
Please, calm down.
I'm sorry.
How exactly was I
supposed to save you?
I was desperately giving you
signs to oppose the motion
while it was up for vote,
but you just didn't
seem interested.
Are there any objections
to the majority vote?
Are there any at all?
Is anyone opposed
to the idea?
Come on, anyone?
If just one person objects,
then it goes up for discussion.
Sorry, I had no idea.
Please Fujioka. You have
to let me be on your team!
If I'm with you,
then maybe your
peace of mind
will help me.
And I can remain
more calm!
Class Rep!
And one more thing, you can't
tell the Hitachiin brothers!
Is someone a fraidy cat?
Oh, there you are.
We're about to
choose groups.
So do you have any idea
who you'd like
to have on your team?
Yeah, the four of us'll be one!
Great. Then you guys
are Team B, alright?
Sounds like fun,
right Class Rep?
This is a nightmare!
It's all over now.
Hey Kaoru, tell us
the story about
the Evil Clock Tower Witch.
One Halloween many years
ago, a girl dressed in
a witch costume,
fell to her death from
the tower.
And now--
--Whoever sees her ghost
on Halloween Night--
--Will be cursed forever!
No! Please stop it, you guys!
Knock if off. The point
is to scare someone not
on your team.
Why don't you save
that dumb shtick
for somebody else?
But no one's come yet. We're
tired of waiting around.
Hey, not so fast.
Look Class Rep. Cool huh?
I borrowed this book
from the library:
"Surefire Methods for
Coping with Anxiety."
Fujioka.
Now let's have a look,
shall we?
"The three cardinal rules
for dealing
with anxiety are as
follows. First--"
"Pretend everything's okay.
Second: whistle a
cheerful little tune.
Thirdly: repeat to yourself
'I'm brave'."
Are you kidding me?
None of those things
actually work!
Call me the Captain of All
Cowards - you can scream it
from the rooftops,
just get me out of here!
Really? Even if it means
Kurakano will think
you're a big chicken?
Whoa? Wait a minute.
What's going on
with you and Kurakano?
No! It's not like that!
We're just friends!
I've known her
since we were little -
None of this has
anything to do with it!
Fine, fine. We understand.
Funny how you had
told us you didn't want
to throw your
weight around-
-when the reason you agreed
to any of this is because
you didn't want to look
like a fraidy cat.
That's not it, that's not the
reason why I couldn't oppose it.
I--It's just--
That sounds like so much fun!
Kurakano.
Well she had her heart set on
this tournament. I didn't want
to let her down so
I couldn't say no.
You mean?
Oh crap! He's totally pure!
He's got a heart
of gold, Hikaru!
Our powers are nothing
against his wholesomeness!
So, does this mean
we have to help him now?
Did you see that?
That creepy shadow just now,
outside the window?
Aw come on!
Not you too Fujioka!
Knock it off, would ya?
No way. It's a sneak attack
from those A-team hacks.
Hey! It's not your turn guys!
Follow the rules!
My skull.
Yeah, you show 'em.
Could it be
The Clock Tower Witch?
Why did you kick--
--my skull?
Who's there?
I'm Frankenstein.
I'm the Wolfman!
Class Rep, slow down!
I can't keep up!
My fright strategy was
perfection itself.
Kyoya, you're not
joining in on the fun?
I'm not.
Damn it.
They've locked us in.
Ow! This was supposed to be
a tournament, not a hunt!
Kaoru! Where is he?
I've got to find Kaoru!
Hey! Cut it out! Stop thrashing
around like an idiot!
I can get us out of this
with my sewing scissors.
Wow! Even you have a
feminine side. Impressive.
And just what is that
supposed to mean?
You've got a smart mouth.
What do you mean
"I've got a smart mouth"?
Kaoru has one, too, you know.
Dream on. Not when he's all
by himself he doesn't.
Unlike you. When you're alone
you only get worse.
Believe me.
Oh yeah?
Now hold still for a second.
What are you doing?
Grow up. This is the
only way I can reach
where I need to cut.
I know it's
awkward but it'll
only take a minute.
No. It's alright.
Take your time.
I can't allow this!
Patience, Tamaki.
The payoff is yet to come.
It's hopeless.
There's no one outside.
Looks like the A-team got
a little overzealous, huh?
Which one are you?
I'm Kaoru. Are you scared?
Well not anymore, no.
My nerves kind of shut down.
Man. Our plans are completely
shot. Such a shame.
We even had it all
figured out,
down to the last detail.
We had worked out
a plan to frighten
Kurakano half to death
and then let you come
charging to her rescue.
Wow, you'd do that for me?
That's really thoughtful
of you. But I don't
stand a chance.
There's someone else she likes.
Haruhi!
While it's true, Fujioka
doesn't seem to feel
the same way quite yet,
I'm positive that it's
only a matter
of time.
Yeah, that's not going to
happen, I can promise you that.
Why not?
It just won't.
Still, this may sound weird
but I don't want to risk
changing anything right now.
'Cause things are perfect.
Just being on the committee
with her is such an honor.
If this is as good as
it's going to get,
I'm still grateful.
So in other words, you've cast
a spell on the carriage.
And maybe you're right,
Class Rep. Keeping things
the way they are
wouldn't be so bad.
I'm sure that's what the
boss had in mind when he
put a spell on his
own carriage.
We're like a family to him.
He doesn't want
that to change.
Back when we were children,
neither the boss nor Hikaru
and I had many
friends to speak of.
Now he just wants to enjoy
what he has for as long
as he can.
I can't blame him.
Uh sorry but you've lost me.
But still, one of these days,
it'll all turn back into that
same ol' grubby pumpkin again.
Kaoru! Are you in there?
Kaoru!
Hikaru!
--Kaoru!
--Hikaru!
So what happened
to Fujioka?
Oh yeah, that's right.
Kinda lost track.
What's wrong with you?
I get us out of the net
and you go tearing off
by yourself?
Sorry.
There they are!
We've been so worried
about the four of you!
Why did you leave
your post in the middle
of the tournament?
We called off the whole thing
to go looking for you.
Wasn't that you guys
trying to scare us?
We didn't do anything.
What is it?
Outside by the window--
--there's a dark figure!
They sure got us.
Nekozawa is such a jerk.
How did we not know
that was Belzenef?
I heard.
You're really a fraidy-cat,
aren't you Kazukiyo? But you
still agreed to the
tournament just to be nice?
Um, yeah. Sure. That's it.
I think that's so
unbelievably sweet of you.
Would you look at that. I guess
the spell on the carriage
can't last forever after all.
What do you mean?
What's wrong with you?
I get us out and you go
tearing off by yourself?
Sorry.
Well, since you ran towards
me in that situation,
I suppose everything's
alright for now.
Nothing, nothing.
Just my own private joke.
Let's get out of here.
Still.
One day Hikaru will realize
he wants to take the
next step on his own.
When that happens.
I don't know what I'll do.
Huh? Mori-senpai
has an apprentice?
Wait a minute -- the
apprentice is from the
Kasanoda Syndicate?
Are you serious?
Next time, "Mori-senpai Has
an Apprentice Candidate"
The Ouran Host Club will
be waiting for you.
We'll see you then.