Once upon a time,
a little girl was sent to an institution
before she was one year old
because of her super intelligence.
She would learn many new things there
like how to walk and how to speak.
It was then that she was introduced to games as well.
She was made to play many games
they called intelligence tests,
but they were so boring that she didn't
enjoy them no matter who she played with.
And then after two years had passed,
she was reunited with a woman
whom she was told was her mother...
as well is a boy who was seven years older than her.
The boy told The adults whatever they wanted to hear
and grinned at everyone with a fake, empty smile.
The girl said to him, the first words
she had spoken in a long, long time...
You seem so empty.
So, you want to play a game?
Who's Sora?
Blank...
Blank does not..
Blank does not...
Oh, dear, you must've had a really bad dream.
I'll bring you a glass of warm milk. Does that sound okay?
No, no!
He was with me! He's always been with me!
That's why...
Shiro.
Shiro!
It's cold.
Master? That's where you were.
Dolly was panicking and said that you ran off
somewhere, so I was wondering what could have happened.
Jibril.
Yes, can I help you with something?
Tell me the names of your masters.
Huh? Is this some sort of game?
I don't know why you would‐
Answer me!
You are my only master.
Then who was it that made me your master?
Well, it was you, of course.
But... Then who told Stephanie to fall in love with them?
It was you, Mistress Shiro.
Who found out about the Eastern Federation's games?
You, Mistress Shiro, with the help of
what Dolly's grandfather left behind.
It was all you.
I was charmed by your unparalleled
brilliance right from the beginning.
That's why I decided to obey you, Master.
Obey me?
Yes.
Only you, Mistress Shiro, Queen of
Elkia, and representative of Imanity.
So she's saying that there was somebody else besides her?
But there's no sign of this somebody.
I expanded my range of inquiry to the entire
city in addition to the castle to no avail.
Yeah, no one in the protest demonstration
seems to know anything about him either.
Yes, I was afraid of that.
It seems as though master must have
played a game with someone unbeknownst to us.
She then lost and had her memories altered.
That's impossible, there's no one who could...
The Eastern Federation.
Yes, they are capable of that.
Master?
Let's play a game.
Uh...
A game?
Yes, we can just bet the false memories
that have been implanted inside you, okay, Miss?
False memories?
And I know it's very rude to ask of you,
but would you please lose?
All right then, that's a check.
False memories.
But they... seem so real.
Are they true or not?
Is that why they're disappearing?
Shiro...
They say anyone can change their fate.
Wonder if that's true.
They're all...
all disappearing.
If someone decides they want to
fly, will they suddenly sprout wings?
I don't think so. You can't change what you are.
You can just change how you do things.
Sora?
You have to make your own way.
You have to create a way to
fly even while you stay the same.
That's how you survive.
Let's think of something together, okay,
a way to give you wings.
No need to hurry.
They're all...
fake memories...
all of them, lies.
If they disappear, I'll feel...
"You're... Blank"?
Master?
Blank does not...
Blank doesn't...
Blank does not lose!
Why... did you win, Mistress Shiro?
He's real! Sora is real!
I know! I know he's real!
Shiro...
Master, please calm down.
He's real! He is real!
Just slow down, Master. Try
to think through this logically.
You're right.
I mean, it absolutely does make
more sense to think he doesn't exist,
but somehow I feel in my heart that he really does.
But Dolly, he doesn't.
Besides, I couldn't imagine you
losing. So it must be something else.
Oh, Steph.
Then where is he?
Yeah, he's gotta be here somewhere!
There must be some reason why this
happened, some reason why we can't remember.
Come now, you're being ridiculous,
This doesn't make sense.
Hey, guys?
What did we do yesterday?
Uh... yesterday?
I was busy dealing with the demonstrations.
After that, you played a game in the throne room.
That was the day before yesterday, the 19th.
Let me rephrase my question.
Do you remember where you were two nights ago?
Okay, let's see, now think, what
was I doing the night before last?
Well, um, I huh?
I can't remember.
Right, none of us can.
Huh...?
Now let me see.
Mmm!
Well, this is... different.
Well, Steph, do you like this or not?
Excuse me, how am I supposed to respond to that, exactly?
You don't like it?
Even though I made you fall in love with me?
Not really.
So you're saying that someone other than you
must have told you to fall in love with them, right?
Yes, it was my brother Sora who told her that.
Okay, but didn't you already decide
that he existed without this test?
Yeah, that's right, so why did you just
totally grope me if you already knew that?
I, uh... wanted to be sure.
Thanks a lot, Steph. You were a big help.
Oh, sure.
Then let's think hard about this.
If Sora actually exists somewhere,
then how could he have disappeared?
He wasn't just taken away. Our memories of both him
and the last day and a half have all vanished, too.
A large‐scale magic spell could conceivably do something
like that, but it would've left some traces of being cast.
What if it was a game?
A game?
What if the rules are altering our perception of reality?
It's possible because of the pledges.
Hmm, if the game involved Imanity's representative,
then I suppose it's possible that the rules
would be able to affect the entire race,
but it shouldn't work on Jibril, should it?
No, because Sora's my master now,
he should be my representative, too.
We can assume I'm under the same effects as well.
Okay, I guess that makes sense, but if that's the
case, then what kind of game are we talking about?
I don't know.
But I know what... Sora said to me.
You know that I believe in you.
Shiro, never forget the two of us are always one.
Sora would never leave me all by myself.
So...
Shiro, where are you?
You're still there, right, Shiro?
Sora?
Huh?
Would you just hold on to me somewhere,
anywhere that I can still feel?
I'm losing my mind in here.
Sora!
Shiro?
It's time to use every last brain cell I've got.
What's really going on here?
Come on, Sora trusted me with this.
I've got to try and use all the memories I still have.
Sora said that we're always together,
so he must be here somewhere.
And he said that the game is
always won before it even begins.
He was trying to prepare me for this.
He told me the two of us are not like comic book heroes.
No, I've got to think harder! Harder!
He said he was going to get the last piece we needed.
Get the piece we needed?
Then this game is to get us something we
need before we can face the Eastern Federation.
A tool? A strategy?
An observer. An Elf?
He's going to get an Elf, but how?
Challenge Elven Gard? Kurami?
No, Kurami doesn't believe in Sora.
She'd never agree to help us.
What if the game...
was to steal each other's being?
Shiro! Shiro!
A game to steal each other's existence?
That's right.
These 32 stones collectively make up your existence.
They're individually numbered
and ranked in order of importance.
Their priority is assigned to them by your subconscious.
So in other words neither of us can
consciously know which of these stones
constitutes which part of ourselves
until our opponent has taken it away.
What importance does your subconscious
place on that elf next to you?
Or your arms, legs, nerves, or memories, for that matter?
In the end, your very existence is taken
and no one will even realize that you're there.
In other words, you'll disappear.
Are you serious?
Uh‐huh.
Pledge number five, the challenged party
has the right to decide the rules of the game.
If you don't like it, the game is off.
What do you say?
Kurami.
Fiel, you realize this man is saying that
he's willing to bet Imanity's race piece?
We can't simply ignore that.
Look, honestly, I was sort of hoping that we'd
be able to possibly reconcile after what happened.
Oh, we can reconcile but to do that,
first you gotta trust me and give me that elf.
You know that's not gonna happen.
I guess you're right.
What exactly are you betting?
Let's say the winner gets the right
to make two demands of the loser.
One could, for example, make
the results of the game eternal,
erasing the other's existence permanently.
Then they could alter the memories of the
loser's partner to make them their ally instead.
So then what you want to do
here is bet not only our partners
but our existence as well?
That's right.
You are just insane.
Well, then, since I'm apparently out of my mind
already, I'll go ahead and impose one more important rule.
Sora?
Master?
Shiro, are you feeling okay?!
Sora!
Jibril?
How can I help you, Master?
In a game, could you steal someone else's existence?
No, I don't think you could.
It's only possible in a fake world
like the one we used to play word chain.
What if an Elf helped you?
An Elf?
Those disgusting little forest creatures?
Why, during the great war, I easily
destroyed one of their capital cities‐
But could you?
I suppose it is possible.
Gross and weak as they are, those animals do
have some small measure of skill when it comes
to constructing complicated spells at least.
Then what you're saying is that this Sora guy
managed to erase his own existence by playing this game?
Yes.
But if he's been erased, then wouldn't it
mean the game's over and he's already lost?
What else could it mean otherwise?
Yeah, that's true, if he won, he would exist, and
we wouldn't be worrying about this in the first place.
What if it was neither of those?
You think the game's still being played now?
Mm‐hmm.
That can't be.
Jibril, see if you can detect any magic in this room.
I understand, Master.
I woke up here in this room.
Even though my brother and I sleep somewhere else,
this is where I woke up.
Sora always said he would never leave me alone.
You're right, magic is being used here.
But I can't tell from what exactly.
Okay, we just have to search
everywhere until we can find something!
Oh, dear, you just tripped over literally nothing, Dolly.
You aren't obligated to embarrass yourself.
How'd that happen? Something was there.
An Othello disc? Hmm.
That says "three" in the Elf language.
Why are there discs but no board?
Because they haven't been played yet.
If they're still here, then I can play.
Yeah, but even if that's the case,
all we have here are two sets of three discs. There isn't
any way for us to know if we're playing black or white.
It's simple. Sora said that we're one.
The two of us are one player,
and I'm still participating in this game.
This rule is very important.
Each of our partners will play in the game as well.
If one of us can't continue to play,
our partner can play for us.
That's why I still kept some memories.
Then can you see it, the playing board?
I can't.
But I... know what Sora would do next...
What is this? You're deliberately
trying to lose, aren't you?
No, I've set it up so I can still win like this.
How he would lead his opponent on.
Hmm? What happened? Are these were memories?
Does that mean you're making me
steal your memories to prove that
you're not using the magic
abilities of another race to win games?
That's not such a bad answer.
How he would tell me what he wants...
Now he can't continue the game.
I won then, I guess.
Then why is the game still here?
Huh? What is going on? Shouldn't the match have ended?
There's three left.
What parts of Sora do they represent?
How he would deceive his opponent, and then...
how he'd be able to win.
Sora, you're amazing.
Nobody would be able to figure this out.
Nobody but us.
Now I understand.
I know what parts of you are contained in these discs.
Three, the way to win this game.
Two, the absolute faith you have in your little sister.
And the last one...
everything I am to you.
Now please...
come back to me!
SORA!
Oh...
We did it.
Shiro...
Okay! You can punch me if you want!
Give me your best shot! Let me have it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Sora! I should have come sooner!
I can't believe I actually forgot my master.
I'm still so confused.
Kurami!
Please wake up! Kurami!
Can you hear me? Oh, say something.
Now then, since I'm the victor,
it is time for me to make my demands.
Please, please I beg you, you can do whatever
you want with me, just don't hurt Kurami.
Yeah, whatever. Demand number one.
Please, no!
We keep a copy of the memories we stole
from each other and return the originals.
Huh?
Kurami.
Wait, what's going on?
They each get to keep the
memories they took from one another,
but they all get their own memories back as well.
Now Kurami Sora know everything about
each other so there's no need for distrust.
In other words, they can work together without
having to wonder about what the other's motivations are.
This is the last piece that he had been looking for.
Demand number two, I want you, Elf.
Fiel, I'm gonna reserve the right
to alter your memories as I please.
Wha...
Don't worry.
It's fine, Fiel. He only wants one thing from us.
If I'm not mistaken, you need us to spy for you.
Yeah, you got it.
Sounds like we're both on the same wavelength already.
But spies? What does he want us to spy on?
Mmm, oh, I'll tell you later.
After seeing what was in your head,
I changed my mind about you.
You can count on me.
You're amazing, Sora.
Hmm? Aren't I!
Tell me how proud you are of your
big brother. Come on, don't be shy now.
Mm‐hmm.
So proud of you. You're my hero.
Oh, shucks, when you put it like
that, it really makes me blush!
Oh!
Master?
Shiro... are you ready to do this?
Yeah.
I'll be standing by. Any time is okay.
Fiel...
Kurami...
Oh, my God, I was so scared! I'm never doing that again!
What's wrong with them? Are they okay?
They like to put on such a tough show all the time.
But they have a sensitive side, too.
All your base are belong to us.
Shut up!
I know all the memes, yay!