I've noticed some unruly behavior
among the students as of late.
And since you are the school's guidance counselor,
I trust that you'll be stricter with students
and enforce our rules.
Of course!
Yes! You can count on me!
Just trust me, the next time...
That's right!
Becoming the guidance counselor was the first step I took
to growing as a person! I have to do my best!
Oh, my goodness! I can't believe what I'm seeing!
Wait, just calm down. You can do this.
Um. Excuse me!
Uh. What can I do for you, madam?
I'm sorry to bother you, but you see, uh, I was thinking
that it might be inappropriate to eat while walking?
Or something like that.
Apologies!
I skipped breakfast this morning.
And my stomach couldn't wait until lunchtime.
But I shall put this away immediately.
You mean it? Thank you so much!
I'm really glad you understand.
That wasn't so bad. All I had to do was speak up.
Please tell the chef...
...the meal was to die for!
If you don't stop making a scene in the hallway,
you really will die here,
so quit being such a weirdo at school!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I don't think those are allowed?
Hey, Misato! We're headed out!
Coming!
Sasahara! We'll continue this during the lunch break.
Don't you forget it!
The principal was right about the unruly behavior.
My apologies.
I'm sure she meant no harm.
She tends to be a bit dramatic.
Don't mind her.
Uh, okay. I guess, if you say so.
Oh! One more thing!
Question.
What do you call that frilly
piece of cloth around your neck?
Ah, you mean this?
Yes, I have to say, it looks rather dashing.
We live our ordinary lives, day after day, in succession.
Each hour can be considered a miracle in itself.
Uh.
So, you see. Each moment should be truly savored.
So, uh, you never actually said
what that frilly thing was.
Ahh! That's a good one!
Now, then. I bid you adieu, madam.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
...Go+Soccer club is a club that plays Go and Soccer.
Both individually, and at the same time.
Excuse me, Nakanojou! A moment please?
Yes. How can I help you?
Uh, well, you see, thing is...
I was just thinking that your haircut
might be a little too extreme for school.
Uhh...
Uh. I mean, just by a little bit!
On second thought, it's not all that bad.
It's all I have.
Hey, I'm really sorry if I offended you.
I was only saying--
My hair.
My hair doesn't grow out on the sides!
Green light!
Still green light.
Green light...
And red light!
Everyone went home already.
Um, what are these?
Those are green plums.
I thought it might be kind of fun
if I tried pickling some of them at home this year.
Pickled plums are so sour.
But they're very healthy for you.
Plus, if you put them inside of rice balls,
it'll keep the rice from going bad.
Ah! Yum!
Hey, Nano!
I think not.
Gah! You say no, but I haven't even asked anything yet!
We bought you plenty of snacks
the other day, and I thought
I made it clear that we're not going to buy any more
of them until you finish the
ones you already have at home.
Are you listening to me?
Remember we came here for a purpose.
To shop for... uh...?
Sakamoto.
Right. We told Sakamoto that this grocery trip
was to get him food, so we can't get distracted by...
Whoa that's giant.
Um, 'Scuse me.
Yes? Anything I can help you with?
That thing up there. Is it new?
Yes, our snowman just came in this morning.
It's the only one we have in the whole store.
Can I eat it?
Well, I guess it wouldn't be too different
from a shaved ice dessert.
Oh, it's cold!
And cheap, too!
Gonna buy it?
Uh. No, I was just wondering how much it was!
Check out the snow man.
I want it.
Uh.
Young lady.
Yes ma'am?
If you're not going to buy that
snowman, please give it to me.
Okay, I'll take it!
So, I don't get to buy anything,
but you can buy whatever you want?
You're such a big meany.
Listen. It's not like that.
Yes, it is! You wouldn't let me get my favoritest snacks,
but you picked up a snowman just cause he's cute.
It's not fair! I wanna buy stuff too!
Okay, fine, I give-- you can get one snack.
Do you mean it?
All right. We're good.
So that's why you ended up buying that thing.
Uh-huh! It's cute, it's cold, and I like how it feels.
Hmm...
Okey-dokey, here's some more.
Yay!
Nano, I need more snow! Right away!
Coming right up!
You two are unbelievable.
Anyway, where's the food you got for me?
Oh.
She forgot my food.
That's snow way to treat a cat.
Talk about a cold shoulder.
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and a one, two, three! ♪
Up and away...
The screw!
Uhh...
That's not it.
Okay! It's time to turn in your tests!
Say what?!
That was a bald cap.
Figuring out what people want
is no simple task.
Because all people want different things in life.
Instead, focus on what your own goals are.
That can be easier to grasp.
From there, do the best you can and have faith.
That's all we can do.
We work hard, and hope life takes us down the right path.
Still green light.
Green light...
And red light!
Are we still not done?
I got sent out to the hall again.
Huh?
I'm finally starting to get used to this body.
Just looking at them is making me hungry.
♪ Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair ♪
♪ Fuzzy Wuzzy... ♪
What're these?
These are called pickled plums! They're quite delicious!
Oh.
Huh? Uh!
You can't eat them yet!
They won't be ready for a little while!
Hey, Sakamoto! Come play with me!
Oh, a foxtail.
Come on, pretty kitty. Here, Sakamoto.
That's "Mister" Sakamoto to you, ya little brat!
Or did you forget already?
Oh yeah, I did forget. Sorry, Sakamoto.
Now you're just doing it on purpose!
I just forgot again!
But I promise I'll remember it next time, Sakamoto.
Do you mock me, child?
All right, I'm off to the store!
See ya later!
Jeez. You two really need to learn some manners.
You've got no respect.
Sorry, Sakamoto. I'm not doing it on purpose.
Could you, for once, add the "mister"?
Want some gum? Would that help, Sakamoto?
How many times do I have to tell you
before you get it through your thick skull?
And what makes you think you can give gum to a cat--?
Would you cut it out?
I'm sorry.
Listen up. As I've explained before,
I'm older than you in human and in cat years.
And as your elder, I deserve respect...
in the... form... of... the title "mister"...
So, uh...
You gotta... do the thing.
You know... what I said before... about the...
...you know, name and the...
What?
Can I go and use the potty?
Yeah! Sure! Go ahead!
Potty time!
And she took it with her.
As I suspected,
those two kids are the only ones living in this place.
Now I get it.
That explains why they're so undisciplined.
So, if I'm older than both of them,
I guess that means I'm the oldest in the entire house.
Heh. So be it. Seems like I'll have to step in
as the parental figure they're lacking.
Hm? This is quite the unusual family
I've been brought into.
Oh man, this thing is so much fun!
Hey, Sakamoto. What are you up to?
Crap! If she finds out
I was playing with an eraser,
she'll lose her respect for me!
The respect I worked so hard for.
I was, uh, taking a nap?
Cats sure do sleep a lot.
Anyway, that's the way things are.
The way things are?
Yup. Now you're getting it.
You've gotta get a grip on the basics first.
Like... learning how to respect... your... el... ders!
Oh man! This is so much fun!
Ah! Sakamoto! Do it again!
Do it again! Come on, the jump flip!
Hey! Don't forget the basics!
I told you to call me "mister" Sakamoto!
I'm home!
Hooray!
Don't you ever knock, Mom!
Green light!
Red light!
It's like she begging me to make a joke
about how she's reading weird stuff.
Well, I guess I'll take the bait.
That book your reading is going undercover!
Yuuko.
Please don't ever make a joke like that one again.
Uhh...
The jokes you make are always so good.
My own aren't nearly as funny when compared to your jokes.
Uhh...
Well, I don't always come up with the jokes on my own!
Sometimes, the jokes come up with me!
Y'know! Like just now when you had your books
stacked up weird, it's almost like you were asking for it!
But, like. Thing is...
I wasn't sure you'd think it was funny.
Really, you weren't sure?
Are you being honest when you say that?
Uh? Huh...?
I figured that you would understand.
Huh?
I thought you'd catch on
to what I was doing since you're so intelligent.
I had no idea you saw me in that way!
I mean, I'm flattered you think so highly of me!
And it's so good to know there's someone out there
who thinks I'm trustworthy.
Trustworthy?
I'd rather not bring trust into this.
And I don't think we should speak to each other.
After all, we aren't friends anymore.
Hm?
We're best friends.
We don't need words to convey our feelings.
You mean it?
Come on! Don't be silly!
Even though we're best friends, we can still talk, right?
But... Mai...
I would prefer it if you didn't touch me so frequently.
Uh. Um.
All right then.
Sorry.
Please stop it.
You keep saying things like that and I can't help it.
Huh?
I can't stop myself from liking you even more.
Huh...?!
Um, uh, hey, it's not a big deal!
Of course you like me! Because we're friends!
Best friends, right?
High-Five!
No, it's not like that at all.
Huh?
I do like you as a friend,
but I also like you like you as more than that.
Sorry. I just... can't really explain it.
Well, I... That's, uh...
What the heck is going on?
I knew something was up!
She's talking way more than usual!
Come to think of it, she was the one who suggested
that we go somewhere alone today!
Did she want to confess her feelings?
But why, and since when?
How long has she felt this way?
Hey, uh, Mai, I just have a little something to clear up.
Uh. The thing is, I don't know what to say!
This is all happening so fast,
and we're both so young, and we're only in high school!
We've got our whole lives ahead of us!
I think we might be rushing into things!
You know that I was just kidding, right?
That was super, ultra, great, delicious, wonderfully
hard to understand!
Why would you do that?!
You totally had me going there!
Now you're saying it was all a joke?!
I see.
Uh...?
You're usually so perceptive to these kinds of things,
so I was expecting that you would figure out
what I was up to and play along.
Well, I...
I had a feeling you were up to something.
You're a liar.
Not exactly. I knew that something was off,
it just took time for my brain to process the signs.
I almost had you figured out, too.
You ended up dropping the act before I could put it
all together and start playing off of you.
Didn't you just say that I totally had you going earlier?
Huh?
I hate being lied to more than anything,
so you can stop making excuses.
Uh...
Sorry.
Chill out I'm still just joking with you.
I don't even know what to believe anymore!
So you didn't notice then?
You couldn't catch the other joke I made?
I don't care, just tell me what it was!
It was at the very beginning when I said
I thought you were smart.
You went along with it,
so I just kept on messing with you.
That was why?!
Well, at least I can understand
why you made that first joke.
It's me!
Your friendly neighborhood apartment complex!
Can you believe I'm over 40 years old now?
I guess you could call me the land lady.
That's got a raunchy ring to it, doesn't it?
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 5.
Look forward to it!