Hey, so, idea.
Yeah?
We should throw Nano a surprise birthday party!
Oh, sure! When do you wanna do it?
Today.
Today?
You could give us more of a heads up
before planning this stuff.
My b!
'Kay.
I got nothin'.
What can we put together in a day?
Well, I honestly don't even know
if today is her actual birthday,
so I wouldn't sweat the details too much.
Then what's the point?
Because.
Because what?
That's what makes it a surprise!
I guess so?
Hakase, too.
Huh?
We should also celebrate Hakase's birthday today.
Ooh! Yeah, sure!
Knocking out two birthdays at once? I like it!
Now that I think about it,
I guess surprise parties can still be fun for everyone,
even if it's not anybody's birthday.
Okay, I got it!
We should all go pick up a cake
for the party after school today!
Let's do it!
Does that sound good to you, Mai?
I left my purse at home.
Oh. That's all right.
Yuuko and I can split it then.
I actually forgot my wallet, too.
Please, Mio! We're beggin' ya!
Uh...
I suppose I never paid you back
for all that money I lost at the amusement park.
So, don't worry about the birthday cake.
It's on me.
I'm gonna go tell Nano about
the awesome party we're throwing for her!
It's supposed to be a surprise!
Close one.
I forget how dumb you can be.
Uh... Yeah?
Well, at least Koujirou didn't shoot me down.
Wow!
Hey! I wasn't shot down!
Oh, yeah? Then why'd you run away crying?
I, uh...
I was just surprised by the sudden turn of events
and needed a hot second to process it all, 'kay?
Koujirou having a girl on his arm doesn't mean anything!
And I haven't even tried to tell him how I feel yet.
Unless he turns me down to my face,
I won't give up on him!
He's the guy that I love! Got it?
So, deal with it! Okay?!
All right!
Do I have everything? Yup!
Hakase! I'm heading off to school now!
Nano!
Yoink!
Huh?
What'd you do that for, Hakase?
Because! I made you a little guy
so I'm taking the big one off!
Hang on. What exactly do you mean by "little guy"?
Here, I can show you.
It's, uh.
Are you saying that my back could be smooth
with this "little guy"?
Uh--yeah, I guess.
But this little guy can do more than just that!
It can, uh... Wait, uh...
--Nano? --Yes?
I kinda lost it.
Oh, no!
What's the matter?
Why are you being so rowdy
this early in the morning?
You little brat!
Stop leaving these weird traps all over the place!
Sakamoto broke the little guy I was gonna give you!
Wha?
Wait! Hang on, I, uh...
No. It was an accident!
Look! Mean old Sakamoto made Nano cry!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who left it on the ground!
It's not my fault!
I'm gonna go to school now.
Nano! You forgot this!
I, uh...
I can make another one if you want me to.
Would you be able to finish it before I get home?
It's not hard for me to make, so yeah.
Okay!
I'll be back real soon!
Great!
All right, I'm off!
See ya later!
Yeah. See ya.
Oh, my, how bizarre.
Huh?
Vice-Principal!
If it isn't the statue of me that stood in this very place
when I held the position of principal at this school.
Yes. Strange indeed.
I wonder what happened to your
statue, Principal Shinonome.
These young students do the darndest things.
I simply can't understand the
humor behind pranks like these.
It just doesn't make any sense!
Unless there is a reason.
Perhaps I have some secret supporters in the student body.
Vice-Principal!
We finished your delivery!
This is where you wanted us to put the statue, right, sir?
Uh, well, um, you must be mistaken.
Hey wait. Was this... your doing?
Uh--that's ridiculous.
This must be another part of the
prank the students are pulling.
It's quite elaborate, don't you think?
Excuse me, young man,
but could you take this statue away as well?
Huh? You really want us to take this dinky statue back?
Dinky?!
Understood, sir!
We'll be hauling this ugly thing
out of your sight immediately!
Ugly?!
Hey! We gotta load up this pathetic-looking one, too!
It's okay, Vice-Principal.
Don't take it personally.
We can put it right next to the crappy one
we already have on the back of the truck!
What?!
Huh? It's unlocked.
Hmm?
Oh, wow, I didn't expect you to be so early.
I thought I'd be the first one here.
I took the blackbird and everything.
So, did you come in to take part in the morning practice?
Well, I...
I, uh... just, uh...
I did!
What? Really?
Yes.
I should've known that I would end up
buying both of your lunches, too.
Sorry!
Nah, since you both forgot your wallets,
I really don't mind it.
Wow! That's so generous of ya!
You're the bestest!
Whoa. I hit too hard.
Yeah. You should really be more careful, you know.
That's my bad!
That's my head.
Sorry, I didn't see you there, Mai!
Me neither.
Oh! By the way, did you end up asking Nano
if we could come over to her place later today?
Crap! I totally forgot to!
So, I'll run and tell Nano about
her surprise party right away!
No! It's supposed to be a surprise!
Just ask if we can hang out at her house later!
I knew that, silly!
I don't think that you do!
Fine! I'll ask her myself!
Come on! I said I'd do it!
Yeah, and that's the problem!
Aww, you can trust me!
I really can't!
I can ask her.
Uh--wait! Hang on, Mai!
Don't worry about it! Just gimme a chance!
'Kay, I'm gonna go find Nano and ask about the thing!
I totally got this, guys!
I'm sorry!
No worries.
Godspeed!
Uh, yeah, sure, thanks.
And I'm really sorry! And, uh, bye!
Aw, man!
But I didn't want coffee.
Oh! That was my bad!
No big deal.
I get you're probably in a hurry right now.
I am! But I'm still sorry!
Come on!
Uh?
Um! Excuse me!
No running in the hallway!
Rainbow.
I just can't believe that it's actually over!
Found it!
Huh? Huh...
Aw man, that one stung.
--Yuuko! --Huh?
You're not hurt, are you?
Oh! You're just the person I was looking for!
You were trying to find me?
Yeah! I actually wanted to--
Wait! That's not--!
I, uh...
Whoa! Are you okay?
I didn't hurt you, did I?
Oh. Don't worry. I'm all right.
Really? Well, that's good.
And, uh, this isn't what you think it is, I swear!
It's a trick I can do!
Anyway! I wanted to ask you
if me and the others could come
over to your place later today.
Huh? Sure you can.
Oh! Also, it's--!
Heh, heh, heh. I can't tell you anything else,
'cause it's a surprise!
Um, okay.
We'll see you later then!
Yeah. Sure.
It looks like I'll have to buy more
if Yuuko and the others are stopping by.
Can you believe we made it to the end?
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and one, two, three! ♪
What the heck?
This dumb pumpkin is too strong!
I'm so sick of that kid.
Why does she always pull that--
Taisho?
Is that you, Taisho?
It is!
Wait! Nakamura?
I've been looking all over for you!
I'm glad you're okay.
Why are you running?
Don't you remember who I am?
Of course I remember!
That's why I'm running!
Taisho, time for dinner.
Here.
Hm? What's the matter, boy?
Are you not hungry? Huh? Huh.
What's wrong, Taisho?
Time for your bath.
And now.
Bad kitty!
Oh, no. I have to hurry or I'll be late.
Okay, Taisho. I'll see you when I get home.
Bye.
Wow! Close one.
Gotta run.
Taisho!
Where'd you run off to, kitty?
Just get out of here already!
Oh! Ms. Nakamura!
Nice to see you!
Uh, Nano?
Perfect! I'm sure she can do something!
Is something the matter?
You looked like you were searching...
It's like she's a robot moth
drawn to my flames of science!
But... I can locate Miss Shinonome
any time I want at school.
Right now, my cat takes priority.
Sorry to bother you,
but have you seen a black cat around here?
Oh! You wouldn't happen to own a black cat, would you?
What a fun coincidence!
Well. Sort of.
He ran away a while ago.
I'm sorry.
I have a black cat, too, so I can sympathize.
That so?
Would it be okay if I helped you look for him?
Of course.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Not at all!
You are useless!
So, can you tell me more about your cat?
I heard you call out a name earlier.
What was it again?
It's Taisho.
That's an interesting name for a cat.
Huh?
My cat's named Sakamoto,
because that's what was written
on the box we found him in!
That's a weird way to name a cat.
That's true. It really is kind of weird, I guess.
Tell me, is he cute?
Huh?
Your cat Taisho?
Is he a cute kitty?
Heh. What a ridiculous question!
Of course he is.
Well, it's not like she meant to
treat me poorly on purpose.
Then again, if she kept that up,
my day's probably would've been numbered.
Wait, now that I think about it,
that's not any different from how I have it right now!
If I were to compare the two, they're equally bad!
Oh, it's this late already?
I'm sorry about this, Ms. Nakamura,
but I have to start heading home
since this won't stay fresh for very long.
Ah. Sure. That's fine.
When you find Taisho,
would it be okay if I came to visit him?
Of course!
You can visit whenever! Any day! Tomorrow even!
Well, I look forward to it.
Same here!
This--this sucks!
It doesn't matter who I go with, they're both the worst!
Hakase! Sakamoto! I'm home!
Nano!
Here's the little guy!
You really managed to finish it?
Yeah! But Sakamoto stepped on it again!
Sakamoto...
Yoink!
Wait. Did you--?
You're still okay with taking that off?
I'll make another one, quick!
You're the best!
♪ This goes here, and that goes here... ♪
I had no idea that this key would come off so easily.
It wouldn't budge at all
whenever I attempted to remove it by myself.
That was me!
I made it so you couldn't take it off yourself,
but any other other person could do it easy-peasy!
Of course she did.
Plot twist!
Anybody can hook it back up, including you, Nano!
That's an oddly specific feature.
I've been meaning to ask.
How will this new little guy
affect all the features I have?
Huh?
Once you have this new part in,
your big toe won't be able to fly off anymore.
I wouldn't consider it a loss.
That must be Yuuko and the others.
Wha? Yuuko!
Yuuko's here!
Oh, that's right!
I should probably hide this key.
I'm so glad I look like normal person now.
Maybe I'll get along better with everyone
without having to worry so much.
I'll be able to do things normally.
I can just live my ordinary life, doing ordinary things.
Anyway!
I wanted to ask you if me and the others could
come over to your place later today.
I wanna leave it on 'cause it looks cute.
As long as you're happy with who you are,
that's all that matters.
I just wanted to stop by here and tell you that.
But I got distracted.
Nano!
Hey, kid.
Shh! This is the important part!
Let's do it like we practiced!
All right, I got it.
Ready, and...
Hey, Nano!
Ta-da!
We brought a yummy cake for you!
To celebrate your birthday!
Huh? You all did what?
For my birthday?
Wait, how did you even--?
It was part of the surprise. Are you surprised?
Is that cake? I want cake!
Gimme! I want cake! I want it, I want it!
Hang on, Hakase!
You gotta wait your turn!
Be careful with that!
We're all gonna share.
Well, that sucks.
My cake!
What are we gonna do?
Mio spent a lotta money on that!
I brought another one.
Mai!
What the heck?
A shark!
What was that? Do it again!
Nah! This time it's Mio's turn!
I wonder how they found out today was my birthday.
I didn't tell anyone.
Nano!
I finished making the little guy!
Thanks, Hakase!
Honestly, I always felt that this key was inconvenient,
and I really wanted to get rid of it.
But now,
I like it!
This key's part of who I am! Huh?
Now, with this little guy in, you have an extra feature
that makes your key spin around and round
whenever you're genuinely happy in your heart of hearts!
What's the point of that?
Oh! That's right!
Hakase, do ya think you could help me
carry this cake in to the other room?
Whoa! You got another cake?
I'll be right behind you after I make the tea.
Got it! Cake time, cake time, cake time, cake time!
Hakase?
--The cake. --Not another one.
Hey! Be more careful with stuff like that!
Are you okay? Any way I can help?
I just need something to wipe this cake off me!
Right!
I'll put the candle on it.
I wanna do it!
That's no fair!
We can save that for later.
Help us clean all of this up first.
We gotta clean it up before the cake cakes!
Hang on, Mai!
Hang on. What' so funny?
I, um... Uh...
Another one.
No! Stop! One's enough!
I still don't get what's happening!
I did it.
You better not have hay fever.
I'm fine, I just can't stop sneezing.
Don't be silly!
If you wanna stop, you just gotta have the motivation!
I don't understand how motivation
has anything to do with constant involuntary sneezing.
Hmm...
Sometimes, you just gotta do it!
No way.
What a complete idiot.