Nano!
Nano? Hey, Nano!
What is it?
Are you outside?
Yes.
Nano?
Yeah?
Hey, Nano!
Huh?
Looky, look!
I'm a cat, check me-owt!
Meow!
Sakamoto! I'm like you!
I'm a cat, check me-owt!
Check me-owt! See?
Hakase.
I think your cat look is purr-fect!
--Meow? --Hm?
Meow! Checking me-owt?
That's paw-some!
Here and meow?
So a-mew-sing!
You're checking me-owt!
I'm really feline it!
Meow I'm a cat!
You're kitten me!
I'm fur-real!
Meow you're talkin'!
Meow and fur-ever!
It's another peaceful day
at the Shinonome household.
Why is the Earth round?
How do planes and rockets fly?
Why do magnets attract and repel one another?
Every one of those questions can be answered by science.
Our society is infatuated by the afterlife.
Things like ghosts, and paranormal phenomena.
But such stupid stuff couldn't possibly be real!
They can't exist. There's no way.
Which is why...
...I refuse to believe in psychic mediums!
During one of my days off,
I decided to make an eight-hour trek up Mount Osore.
And the closer I got to the summit,
the faster my heart raced.
Was there really a medium up here?
If there was, then where?
What was the point of living in such a secluded place?
Maybe if...
I found one!
All right, good.
I'll say there's a spirit I need channeled.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Um.
Can you to channel the spirit of Soap?
Yeah, sure.
Hello! It's me, Soap!
Brr, ow! Mic test. Check.
Check, one, two. Check, check.
Testing. One, two, three.
What the--?
It feels like something crazy is going on here.
Could there actually be somebody
out there with the name Soap?
Testing. Check. One, two.
Yes, it's me. I'm Soap. Yup, yup, yup, this is Soap.
No. I can't falter now.
If I just keep asking her stuff,
I'm sure she'll end up contradicting herself somehow.
I have a question.
If you're really Soap, then what's your blood type, huh?
Dunno.
Let's try again with someone more recognizable.
Excuse me.
Could you channel the spirit of the great Oda Nobunaga?
Give me a break here, would ya?
She's refusing my request without even trying?
Wait. I'm dealing with an elderly woman here.
She might be overexerting herself.
I'll figure out another angle.
Thank you for your time.
I'm gonna go home.
I don't like criticizing people.
Realizing that alone makes this trip worth it.
Oh, one more thing.
Uh?
That'll be 5,000 yen.
Huh...
Oh?
Mm. Ah--
Ah-chee.
Wha--?
Boys are so weird.
Okay, you ready?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Huh? Wait, what? Huh?
Come on, Mai! Wake up!
You're supposed to bop me on the head when you win!
Didn't I just explain the rules?
You're no fun. That hurts, you know?
It hurts more than actually getting smacked.
All right. Let's try this again one more time.
If you lose, you guard, and if you win, you get to hit.
Wah!
I didn't mean hit me right this second!
Why would you do that?
Because I won the game earlier.
That was earlier! You can't do it now!
Act when the time is right! Live in the moment!
Strike when the iron is hot!
Just be spontaneous or whatever!
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and a one, two, three! ♪
You're Nya-no now!
Whatever, let's try it again.
Fresh start, okay?
Rock, paper, scissors!
She doesn't even care at all!
Do you enjoy making me look like a fool?
She's so not in the mood.
And now I'm not either.
Uh, where do you think you're going?
There it is.
That statue. Where did... you get that?
Carved it.
Oh, thank goodness.
Here I thought it got reincarnated or something!
I'll put this right here.
She looks strangely happy.
Hey, let's forget about that
silly statue and keep playing.
Kay. Rock, paper, scissors!
Uh. I don't think that counts.
Okay, maybe it does!
Unbelievable. She's so vicious.
I'm begging you, Mai! Please cut it out!
Just play by the rules!
And no using that statue as a weapon!
Are you ready now?
First comes a rock. One, two, three.
Uh.
You did it right.
That's it!
You just played the game!
Aw! I knew you could do it all along!
Cool! Let's go for another round!
Ready? And first comes a...
...rock.
God is dead!
God is indeed dead.
What gives?
Why'd you hit me?
We haven't even played the next round yet!
Maybe it's because
I don't really feel like playing.
Oh.
Then can I see your statue thing? Please?
Yeah, sure.
I'm headed to the library to return some books!
Take care of the house while I'm gone!
'Kay!
Huh?
Why does Nano's daruma guy only
have one eyeball filled in?
I know! If I help her out and fix the other eye for her,
I bet she'll really appreciate it!
She'll be so grateful, she might even say that I can eat
all the snacks I want, whenever I want!
Oh... I think I messed it up,
'cause that doesn't look right. Now what do I do?
Nano'll get mad, and...
Uh! What if she gets so mad she takes my snacks away?!
No more snacks for Hakase ever again!
Just put a little this, and a little there, and uh...
Is something wrong?
Uh! I don't know what to do Sakamoto! Look.
At what? Whoa!
What happened to its face? You did a number on that thing.
I was just trying to even out the eyes.
Hmm...
Don't you worry. I know what we have to do.
I'm home!
Gah!
You're on your own.
Sakamoto!
Where are you off to in such a hurry?
Hey, Hakase!
Sorry I took so long,
but I was picking out new books to bring home.
What'd you do while I was gone?
Wait, what the--?!
What's going on with your belly?
Well, uh. You know how it goes sometimes.
What does that even mean?
It's coming!
Wait.
There's no way. You can't possibly be having a child.
I'm having one now! The baby is coming!
O... kay? Are you pulling some sort of prank?
I'm not! I'm bringing your baby brother into the world!
It's your baby brother.
Goo-goo. Ga-ga.
This could be a problem.
Helvetica Standard.
Mio! You wanna play a game?
What kind?
How 'bout we play Kokkuri?
What's that?
Wait. You've never heard of it before?
Nope, never.
Okay then, I'm gonna break it down for you.
You start by drawing a shrine gate
at the top of the paper here.
Then you write Yes and No on the
sides, and the alphabet below.
Okay.
And in some regions, I think you're supposed to draw
a little piece of fried tofu somewhere
on the paper too, but...
Let's stick to the simplified version for now.
Then. You have to make sure to open up
a north facing entrance so the spirits can get inside.
Next, we take a ten-yen coin
and set it on top of the gate we drew at the beginning.
Finally, we both touch the coin with our fingers
and ask it a question.
There's no restriction on what kind of things you can ask
the spirit, so the sky's basically the limit here.
Sure.
And then, without any effort of our own,
spirits will slide the coin around and spell out
the answers to our questions for us.
Really?
Yeah! I know it's awesome, but some things are taboo.
First off, you can't play the game by yourself
and you can't half-ass it.
Because if you do, you might get possessed!
Oh?
You also risk getting possessed
if you stop partway through,
so you gotta commit.
Right, I get it.
Now you know how to play the wonderfully spooky game
of Kokkuri! So, whaddaya say we give it a shot?
Nah, I'm good.
Ahhhh....
So, uh, that concludes the lessons
I have for you today.
Remember that we'll be having a quiz tomorrow,
so make sure you don't forget to study tonight!
What? Can't you push the quiz back?
It doesn't matter if you take it later,
you're still gonna bomb it.
Yeah, probably.
Excuse me, Miss Sakurai?
How can I help you, Miss Aioi?
I just had a question for you, if you don't mind.
Go ahead!
Well, about that English test we had a little while ago.
What is this supposed to be?
The correct answer for that one was "Fly."
No, I'm not asking about the answer.
I'm wondering if you were the one who drew this
low-level looking monster.
Yes, I did. I figured it would help make the test
a little easier if there was a visual aid.
Well then, you have some pretty awesome drawings!
How kind of you. But my drawings aren't great,
so I'm sorry if they were hard to identify.
Uhh...
I know!
How about I give you a hand,
and draw you a picture that you can put on the next exam!
I promise it'll be something really cool!
Sure, okay!
Oh! Hey, Mio!
Hm?
Check it out! My drawing is gonna be in the next test!
Really? Why?
The teacher said she would use it!
I bet you could get yours on there too
if you drew a little doodle of your own right now.
Yeah, I dunno if I'm cut out for something like that.
Huh. What do mean?
I'm just not the greatest.
And besides, I gotta go return this thing.
If you say so! 'Kay!
I think I'm gonna draw a cool-looking dude!
Get a load of this handsome stud!
Wow! He looks so cool!
That's impressive!
I'd say you've got quite the artistic talent there!
Aw, well it's not that amazing.
Oh wait, maybe it is.
I think I'm gonna name my dapper
doodle dude Hubbu Hunkerson.
Wow! That's such a cool name!
None of this is cool!
I dunno guys, I think it should look more like this.
--Feast your eyes! --Edgy!
Wow, amazing! It looks like it's from a manga!
You must put a lot of time and effort
into practicing your art skills.
Well, uh, just a little!
Remarkable! Show me some of your other work!
Uh. I don't think so.
Oh? But why not?
I would love to see more of your stuff.
Um. Well. It's just...
Gimme that thing!
My drawing is way cooler than yours, see?
You straight-up copied me!
You don't know that.
I saw you do it!
"Homage" may be the word you're looking for.
So you're admitting that you copied?!
Wow! That's so cool!
You are so easy to please!
All right, then, prepare yourselves for some of this!
Glasses! Every girl swoons over the cool
and collected demeanor behind those lenses!
Ah, so he wears glasses.
Huh?
Is his eyesight bad?
He'd probably look better if he wore contacts.
You two don't understand anything!
Y'know? I'll add an extra bit!
There we go!
They're hanging under his ears!
You so stole my glasses idea!
Tch. Tch. Tch. They're sunglasses.
Wow! They're so cool!
Are you kidding me?!
Oh, yeah? Then how's this?
A butler! The perfect gentleman
who serves you tea and follows your every command!
He'll treat you like the fine young lady you are!
Huh. Glasses again?
I don't think I understand the appeal.
Maybe you should have taken my contacts idea.
I feel like you're a bit out of touch, Mio. Tell ya what.
I'll show you what being cool is really all about.
Some of this, and some of that.
Check it.
It's floating!
Wait! Hold on a sec! Is he supposed to be driving?
Wow! He's so fast and dangerous!
You've gotta be kidding me!
They don't understand coolness at all!
You wanna see something cool? Then I'll have to show you.
This is a lesson now.
You're gonna see what true coolness really is!
You'll see! You'll all see!
This is the coolest!
Yo.
Uh...
Oh, no.
I'm just kidding!
I kid!
I drew this while listening to jazz.
Good morning!
Oh. Oh, good morning, all knowing master.
Don't you even!
Listen up class!
It's time for this morning's quiz,
so take one and pass it down, please.
Aw man, this sucks.
I was hoping that I could keep my drawing skills a secret
for a while longer, and then I had to go overboard.
All things considered, after going berserk like that,
I should be relieved that what I
drew ended up as tame as it was.
I guess I should count myself lucky.
But I'm sure I won't hear the end of it from Yuuko,
at least for the next few days. That's okay, though!
I gotta look on the bright side! And stay positive!
Yo.
Hurry up and pass it back.
Uhh.
Ready, and... begin!
Yoink! Bang! Zoom!
Hello! It's nice to meet you!
I'm an Onomatopoeia!
Cock-a-doodle-doo! Now you try it!
But don't chicken out!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 6.
Look forward to it!