Was Sasahara was actually asleep in there?
Uh, yeah, totally.
Didn't you see him? He was 100 percent taking a nap.
Ooh, you should go wake him up, Misato.
Huh?
He probably isn't aware that we're
changing classrooms right now, so you should let him know.
That's not my responsibility!
Why should I care?
Come on, don't be like that.
He's your friend, isn't he?
It's not a big deal.
And besides,
you'll probably have the room to yourselves
if you're feelin' feisty.
Huh? What? No way!
Well, have fun, you two!
Tell us the details later!
No! You--!
Why do I have to be stuck with babysitting that idiot?
Just because we've known each other forever.
You should just confess your feelings to him already!
Sasahara!
We're changing classrooms, so would you get up?
We gotta go!
Uh--it's you.
Miss Tachibana.
Just go and grab whatever you need for the next class.
Of course.
I only intended to rest my eyes for a moment,
but it seems as though I must have been lulled to sleep.
I don't give a crap about any of that!
Get your stuff before people get the wrong idea.
Wrong idea? How so?
Just forget it!
I'm so sorry!
I mean, I'm not sorry for doing it,
I'm sorry it that happened, I mean.
Who puts their glasses on a desk anyway?
Misato Tachibana.
Look. Your hand is bleeding.
You don't have to act all nice, y'know.
I broke your glasses,
so you have every right to be angry with me.
Why?
Glasses feel no pain when they're broken.
You're the one who's hurting.
Yeah, no duh!
My hand's bleeding!
That much is obvious!
Fortunately for us,
one of the lenses is still in its rightful place.
As long as the lens hangs on to the glasses, so will I.
It's like the glasses somehow knew...
...and let go.
Follow me.
You really don't--
I know!
But I have to take responsibility.
It's my fault!
You get what I'm saying?
It was totally lame, right?
That's why, uh...
Yeah, totally.
And then I said--uh...
Oh, man, everyone is staring!
I could die. I'm dying!
I am literally dead right now.
But I have to do this.
Sasahara's probably blind without his glasses,
so I have to be his eyes.
It's fine. No big deal.
His glasses are broken, so this isn't weird, right?
Totally, 100 percent understandable.
Yeah! I'm helping out a person in need!
Like a seeing-eye dog.
An embarrassed, dying, seeing-eye dog.
Excuse me, Miss Tachibana.
Uh, yeah?
Before we reach the classroom,
I'd like to take a visit to the facilities.
Wait! So... the bathroom?
The boy's bathroom?
Naturally.
This'll be harder than I thought!
But I can't back down now.
I have to do this for him.
For us!
Fine! I'll go in with you!
But why?
Because your glasses are broken, aren't they?
They are.
Come on! Don't make me spell it out for you!
Your glasses are broken!
So, uh... since it was my fault,
I'm gonna be your eyes for today.
Oh. These are just for style.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I wasn't holding your arm because I wanted to or anything!
There was a bug on your sleeve
and I was just trying to squish it very slowly.
What beautiful weather today.
Uh--
Huh?
Uh--! So, uh,
I know this spicy curry place in Kamakura!
Oh! That's nice!
How spicy do you like your food, Ms. Sakurai?
Oh? Well, uh...
No spice at all.
Same! What a coincidence!
Uh...
So, um... our next class.
We're going to be late.
Wait, Mio!
The classroom is in the other direction!
The other direction.
Try to think of it this way!
Life is just like baseball,
and sometimes you end up striking out!
But you can't stop playing the game!
Sometimes you end up striking out.
Just like baseball.
Let's not jump to conclusions!
We don't even know if those two
are actually a thing or not!
Back me up on this, Nano!
Huh? Oh. Yeah!
What she said!
But, Koujirou...
He couldn't.
He wouldn't.
He did.
Anyway, we should get going. Come on, Mio.
--Mio! --Come back!
Nano! You get to class and buy us some time!
I'll take care of her!
Right!
Mio, wait!
Mio! That's a window!
Mio!
Mio, wait!
Mi-oh!
Mio!
--Huh? --Mio!
Uh! Mio?
Hey! Mio?
Mio! Mio!
--Say cheese! --Wait, Mio!
Mio!
This is my stop.
Mio! Watch out!
Look, Mio!
Mio!
Mio, stop!
Mio! Mio!
Maa fell in the river!
Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio! Mio!
Dammit all!
Mi-o-my!
Dios Mio !
Thank you.
Hey, Mio!
I thought I lost you back there!
I'm fine.
I just need to breathe.
Well, that's good.
Where is he?
This way!
There you are, Maa!
Osamu!
Thank goodness you're safe!
You all right?
Yeah, I think so.
If this lady didn't save me, I'd be in big trouble.
Wait! You again?
From before!
I hope the two of you are aware
that interfering with official police business
is a criminal offense!
But I didn't do anything!
Under normal circumstances,
I would report this directly to your school.
But in this case,
I suppose I can overlook it just this once.
Do you mean it?
Ah, there you are!
I've finally caught up to you and your little pigtails.
I saw your shadow boxing.
And you have a true gift.
Uh...
What about it?
With your talents...
...you could rule the boxing world.
Help! Help! He stole my bag!
Don't think badly of me!
Well! Duty calls!
Come to the station later
and you'll get a commendation for your help!
Here, lady. This is for you.
Thanks.
--Osamu, that okay? --Yeah!
Whenever you're ready,
please visit me at my gym,
and then your journey can begin.
Oh, no! Mio, you lost your English textbook
during all that madness!
Mio?
Rejected before I could confess.
Rescued a child while running from my own troubles.
Received an award and a kite.
Got scouted by a boxing coach.
In a way, life really is just like baseball.
I have to keep playing the game.
Huh?
Isn't that what you told me before?
Who knows what'll happen.
So keep going.
That right?
Huh? What's right?
You get it.
I just realized
that daydreaming is totally free.
Damn. I completely lost track of her.
I was hot on her trail
when she was running around the school,
but I took my eyes off her for a moment,
and she suddenly slipped away!
Huh?
A remarkable and surprising feature!
I must know more about your advanced functionalities,
Nano Shinonome!
Now then, I've traveled this far.
Perhaps I should try locating her home.
Hmm, on second thought,
it might be best to tread carefully.
I'll continue my pursuit for knowledge tomorrow
and retreat for the time being.
It's hiding in plain sight!
I've discovered this house completely by chance. Finally!
My first stroke of luck since I started this mission!
No, this more than mere luck!
This is more like, um, what's the word...
It's like, uh... I can't think of it!
I'm too caught up in the thrill of the moment!
To think, the genius who built her
could be in that very building!
Nano's blueprints could be mine to study her every detail!
For science!
What is this strange pounding in my chest?
It's like a hootenanny!
Like former professional wrestler cowboy Bill Watts
is beating on my heart himself!
If this is indeed the house of her creator,
then there's no telling what sort of traps there may be.
If I am to infiltrate this place,
I must be extremely cautious
and pay close attention to my surroundings.
Can I help you, lady?
I'm compromised!
Oh, no!
I've been spotted by the home's surveillance robot!
The build quality looks lower than Nano's,
but he's likely made with the same advanced technology.
If it determines that I'm a threat,
he'll undoubtedly dispose of me!
I have no choice!
I must show that I mean no harm!
What are you doing on the ground?
Compromised again!
So, I heard that goat of yours
carried an injured old lady to the hospital last week.
Yes, he did.
Then the reason you bring a goat is because it's
a service animal for emergency situations like that?
Silly.
Yeah. Well, I'm not the one who rides a goat.
Here you are.
I can't believe they got the jump on me.
I was trying to infiltrate the Shinonome home,
but a warm, hospitable welcome was not what I had in mind.
However, I can see through this ruse.
I'm on to their tricks.
For example, this tea.
I'm certain it contains some sort of drug
that will erase my memory the moment I drink it.
And this room may seem ordinary,
but I'm sure I'm being watched.
What is that?
It has a terrifyingly concerning aura.
Such random placement.
And those painted-on sunglasses can't fool me!
I can't see its eyes, but I can certainly feel their gaze!
I can't make a single wrong move. It's all-seeing!
What's wrong, Ms. Nakamura?
Absolutely nothing!
My apologies!
I drank it all.
I'm a fool.
But if this does wipe my memory,
then I might as well make a stand!
I'll be completely honest with you.
Huh? Sure, go ahead.
I came to your home today
to find out everything I can about you!
Huh?
Wha?
I want to see what you're really like underneath it all!
So, please!
Uh, well, I mean, you're free to like what you like
and pursue what you please, but, uh--
I appreciate it, but I just don't think
any romantic involvement between the two of us
would be the most appropriate thing right now!
You idiot! You misunderstand my words!
You can't just say things like that to me
out of nowhere, you know!
Ah, I'm so sorry! I didn't mean to!
When I said that I wanted to see
what you're like underneath--
Nano?
--Hakase! --Huh?
A child?
It couldn't be her child.
Of course not.
She's a robot after all!
But that garb.
It's that of an intellectual.
Could she be Nano's creator?
So, this child is not the child at all,
but maybe Nano is the child? Yes?
There's no way someone so young could create Nano.
Hello, you can call me Hakase.
Oh, and I created Nano.
Shoulder block!
Hakase!
So it's true.
This child is Nano's creator.
Hey!
Could you get me out of this thing?
I'm tired of all of your pranks!
A homunculus!
The surveillance robot, and the daruma weapon,
and the child creator, and Nano
Shinonome, and the homunculus!
I admit that I was a fool to think that
I was even remotely prepared to
try and infiltrate this home.
But I never could have seen any of this coming!
I must find a chance to strategically retreat
and reformulate my plans.
But...
Knowing that thing is watching has me paralyzed in fear.
I couldn't make an attempt to leave even if I tried!
If I suddenly state out of
nowhere that I have to go home--
I have no other options.
Where's the bathroom?
I must pee.
Uh, okay.
I'll show you where to go--
No need!
If you can give me the directions,
I can find it on my own.
I've completely outwitted you again,
Nano Shinonome.
My plan worked perfectly.
Because of course it did.
I knew how you'd respond.
You see, I capitalized on your weakness.
That's right.
Your kindness leaves you gullible and far too trusting!
And when I return to this deathtrap
you call your humble abode,
I shall turn the tables on you yet.
Just you wait.
As long as I have this big brain of mine,
you'll be completely at my mercy!
Eventually!
Oh. Are you leaving?
Crap!
Uh, well, you see,
I was just asked to mow the
grass on the lawn outside and--
What the--?
Hang on! Don't move!
I'll get help!
No! Wait! Don't go!
Oh, no! They're onto me!
They're going to see me out here
and realize that I lied to them and tried to escape!
Dammit, what is this stuff?
It's robbing me of my movement, my freedom!
She's over here!
Huh? But the bathroom's the other direction.
What is this thing?
Right! Hakase!
Your special glue comes off with water, doesn't it?
If they capture me here, then I'll be done for!
But my studies! My science!
Oh, no!
I must find a way to get out of this literal mess!
Curse you, clever bastards of the Shinonome Lab!
Water!
Somebody help.
Anybody!
Get me out of here!
Oh, I actually have that one.
Really? Do you think I could borrow it?
Yeah, sure. I can bring it tomorrow.
"Who knows what'll happen" and "that's baseball"?
Is that all she said?
Yeah. And she was acting all happy
and laughing and stuff.
Maybe she was trying to be strong
and laugh through the pain.
Getting indirectly rejected by the guy you like
isn't something you just "get over."
Well, she doesn't not look like she's not unhappy.
Wait, run that by me again?
Yuuko, you forgot your homework again, didn't you?
No! Don't be ridiculous!
But wait, I actually did forget, so yeah.
Make up your mind!
You'll find out after the commercial!
Huh?
Wow! That was so random and funny!
Don't you think so?
Fleming?
Wait, rap?
Oh, and Mio.
There's something else I gotta ask you.
Okay.
What's up?
Hey, Yuuko. You know her the best, right?
Can you think of anything that might help cheer her up?
I wonder where they all went.
And here I was hoping we could go out and grab some food
after we were done with class.
What are you guys doing?
Congratulations, young lady!
Please take a spin!
I know it's Yuuko. Cut the act.
Yuu-who?
Never heard of her!
You're so obvious.
I see Nano's key poking out.
It's not like this is a robotic key or anything!
Uh, anyways, everyone who passes through here
has to take a crack at the lottery!
So, step right up!
But why?
I don't really know what you guys are doing.
Well whatever.
Congratulations, we have a winner!
How? I don't get it.
And here's your special prize!
What makes it special?
Just open it and find out!
'Kay?
Your weird practical jokes are
getting harder and harder to understand,
you know that, Yuuko? Uh--
Wonderful! Now please move along!
Thank you for coming!
Bonus prize.
Freshly carved.
Oh, thanks a lot.
This reminds me.
There was something that Koujirou said a while back.
What was it?
Something about our ordinary lives passing us by.
And how it may actually be a series of wonderful miracles.
I think... no, I know... all of that is true.
All right!
I'm gonna go home and draw some manga!
How'd this happen?
It's all your fault we got lost out here!
Apologies. I'll find directions on my "mobile."
Why are you saying that all weird?
Just talk like a normal person!
Wait! Hey!
Are you watching TV on there?
Perhaps you should consume media content
on your "mobile" as well.
My phone isn't that fancy!
I'm Nano's key!
Sometimes I spin!
And sometimes I don't.
Sometimes I even get pulled out!
That's my ordinary life!
And the next My Ordinary Life is the last one!
Look forward to it!