Hellvetica Standard.
My glasses, my glasses, my glasses, my glasses.
My glasses, my glasses, my glasses.
My glasses, my glasses, my glasses!
My glasses!
My glasses, my glasses, my glasses, my glasses, my glasses!
Glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses,
glasses, glasses, glasses, glasses!
I'm feeling crazy,
so watch closely as I do something
you've never seen me do and may never see me do again!
I am a victim of domestic violence!
Well? Did I blow your minds?
And what are we supposed to say to that?
Seems like something you'd do.
Yeah, I think you would've
done that at some point.
Uh-huh, it was definitely a "you" thing.
Well, then the next thing I do will be totally "un-me"
and completely out of character!
I tripped and fell!
That is so something she would do.
Yup. Seems about right.
Daifuku !
Come and get your daifuku here!
Sorry, but...
...could you wear this instead? It's more appropriate.
Come one, come all!
And get some sweet, sweet daifuku !
Sorry again.
Could you try doing this without talking?
They said it was on sale,
but the price was higher than before!
Do you think you could maybe put on a shirt or something?
Are you sulking now?
You're not sulking?
Well, then what's the problem?
Um...
You can use your words to talk
to me if you really need to.
Here I come!
--Yes! --I don't think so!
But I jumped on the mat without touching the bar, so...
Yeah, you made it past the bar.
By going under it!
How many times do I have to repeat myself?
You have to get over the bar!
Sorry.
I'll do it right this time, I swear.
Here, I'll lower it to make things easier.
Take it nice and slow.
And remember the jumping form I taught you before.
Okay!
This is it.
I've gotta at least be able to make it over the bar
when it's that freakin' low.
If I can't even pull this off, everyone'll laugh at me!
Did I do it?
You ding-dong!
Why can't you do the "thing" like I taught you?
Do you just not get it?
Well, I can see me doing a proper Fosbury flop in my head.
Oh, you're flopping all right.
What you're doing is more like a Fosbury... torpedo!
A human... torpedo.
I wouldn't put it like that!
No, wait.
Actually... I think I just did.
I'm not that bad, come on!
Quit joking!
But you are that bad!
Sorry.
Hey, don't apologize.
I'll be right here to help you out until you get it.
You're the one who's always helping me out
with my homework.
And now it's my turn to help you!
I'm gonna stay by your side, no matter what!
Try not to psych yourself out!
Just relax a bit and take your time with it, okay?
You totally got this thing!
I believe in you, Mio!
I've always been bad at sports,
for as long as I can remember.
I hate to break it to you, Mio,
but you're playing the wrong kind of football right now!
I can be just as athletic as anyone else.
But, whenever I have to follow any rules,
everything falls apart!
Get ready!
And... fall!
You're supposed to fall backwards on your back!
But... that doesn't mean I can't change.
I can be better!
I just have to try!
One, two...
There! Huh?
Mio, you are literally spinning out of control!
I don't care how long it takes.
I don't care if I keep failing!
At least there's one thing I know I can do.
I'll never give up!
One, two, three!
Well, almost.
Let's try it one more time.
Yuuko believes in me.
I think I'm gonna take a quick breather, 'kay?
Sure, go ahead.
So, I can believe in me!
I'll give it everything I've got!
I won't quit!
I can be better if I keep on trying!
Great effort can take you to even greater heights.
And thus, the "Torpedo Flop" was born.
The Life of White Tigers!
Check 'em out!
Like... All they do is sleep.
And that one in the front
is giving us a good view of its butt.
Sure is.
They aren't really doing anything,
so there's not much else to look at.
And after all the effort we made to come out! Rude.
I'm just glad we got to see them.
Yeah.
Huh?
Wow!
It's raining!
I gotta go bring in the laundry!
Hey! That's the wrong way!
Huh?
There!
Yay!
Uh--
Looks like it's wet already.
You should still bring it in!
Hakase, Sakamoto, I'm home!
It started pouring out of nowhere,
so I hope you were able to get the laundry
before it got too wet.
It's not my fault! Sakamoto told me to bring it in!
I'm tellin' ya!
It was all the kitty's idea.
He was the one that made me do it!
So what you're saying is,
you knocked the laundry over
while Sakamoto was making you bring it in?
No, he specifically told me to take the clothes and just--
throw them all on the ground.
I did not!
Way to blindside me.
Don't blame someone else for your messes, kid!
But you said to!
I never told you to throw things on the ground!
--Did, too! --I did not!
I wish you weren't a liar!
I'm what?!
Nano.
Why don't we just blame this whole thing on Sakamoto?
That okay?
That is not okay, brat!
No big deal.
I just gotta wash that laundry
again and it'll be good as new.
Oh! Good point!
Guess that's true.
But, I'll never get the time I spend on it back.
As punishment, neither of you
will be getting dinner tonight.
Aww.
Dammit. I didn't do anything wrong!
But it was only Sakamoto's fault!
See? He said so himself!
He confessed! So you can blame him!
All right, then.
Since he owned up to his mistakes,
the only one that doesn't get dinner is you.
Wait! I wanna take some of the blame!
And I can own up to my mistakes, too!
Like how I was the one who tried to
bring in the laundry in the first place
and accidentally knocked it over and got it all wet--
Ta-da!
We'll be having special rice omelets for dinner!
Wow!
The eggs were on sale today!
Wait. I thought I wasn't allowed to have dinner.
Yeah, you're right!
I completely forgot about that!
Well, um... then...
I guess I can let you have the rice omelette for tonight!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
--But tomorrow, you get nothing!
--Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
♪ Swim, swim! ♪
♪ Shark, shark, chomp! ♪
♪ That is what a shark does best! ♪
Mio! Mai! Selamat pagi !
Man, wasn't that clay self-portrait assignment
a huge pain in the butt?
Wait, that project was due today?
Look at that! The great, all-knowing Mio
finally forgot about her homework for once!
Ugh! I thought it was due tomorrow!
Mai, did you do your self-portrait?
Ah, dang it.
So, even Mai forgot about it!
You don't see that every day!
Can you not laugh at this disaster?
But I guess you can say that when it rains,
it pours.
It really...
...started pouring.
Why you little!
What the hell have you three done to my temple?
You must be thieves!
Well, not on my watch!
That was too close!
This must be a curse!
You brought evil spirits to this place!
Just get out of here.
Leave this temple now!
"We should probably go,"
is what the three girls thought,
while being pelted by the late autumn rain.
I'm beggin' you, Pres!
I'm about to have a match with Mr. Takasaki
and we need to find someone to be the referee!
Referee for a Go+Soccer match?
That's right. And if I can beat him,
Mr. Takasaki said that he would become the club's advisor.
I'll win. Trust me!
But how am I supposed to know what to do?
Don't worry.
Just read through that rulebook I let you borrow.
As long as you do that, then everything is gonna be fine!
I have no idea what's going on!
Well, I didn't even open the rulebook,
so I guess I shouldn't be surprised.
But still!
What are they doing?
Is this Go+Soccer?
You wouldn't get it, even if you read the rulebook.
Ogi!
They're using forbidden techniques
most advanced players don't know!
They've reached a level that defies all theory!
Observe his stance with the outstretched arm,
and how it represents the left leg of a Go table.
In contrast, his opponent's stance is the stones.
While it seems simple at a glance,
notice the ball between his feet.
It's just a guess, but I think they're trying...
...to achieve the brilliance of the sun!
Where'd he get all that?
Now I'm even more confused!
It begins!
Oh, no!
And, Beloved!
Hey, Ogi?
What does that even mean?
Be quiet.
Can't you feel it?
The intensity between these two?
If they're not careful...
...someone could die.
Wait, what?
How would that even happen?
I haven't seen such high-level play in some time.
It's quite impressive.
No wonder the air feels so restless right now.
Is that--? This stance.
It can't be!
Unleashing that move in a friendly match?
He's completely insane!
I have no choice.
I can't just stand by and do nothing.
Father, the fated day has arrived.
In the name of all that is just,
shed thy light and become a star!
Ogi Forbidden Referee School! Secret Technique!
Ogi Star!
This is it!
A final love for all!
You're pretty good.
Hey, thanks. You, too.
What the heck?
I kinda just started this little club on a whim.
But now...
...it's gotten crazier than I could've imagined!
Huh?
I break down when no one can see me.
Step on me all you'd like, but I'll never break!
That's right, it's me, Clay!
I can be molded into anything!
But today, I shall take the form
best suited to battle the children!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 20!
All right, kids, bring it on!