Hey, can I ask you something?
Yeah, of course.
Not that this is necessarily a bad thing,
but why do you wear those exact same hair ties every day?
Oh, you mean these?
Hm... 'Cause I wanna.
Sure, but why though?
There's no real reason, it's just my thing.
Okay...
Aw man, I forgot my math notebook.
Hang on! We have a math class today?
Of course we do! That's why we had homework for it.
I'm gonna run back and grab my stuff.
You go ahead!
Well. I didn't do that homework, anyway,
so none of this matters to me.
Oh! Hey, Mai!
Selamat pagi !
Well, well, well, look who it is!
It's my bestest pal herself!
You've finally come to grace me with your presence, huh?
You sure do take things to a whole 'nother level, dontcha?
Y'know! Like a mountain!
Tell me! What's it like being
an actual real-life mountain?
Well, I guess she doesn't like
being called a mountain.
I get it.
You're mad at me.
And I think I understand why.
Yesterday I stole a bite of broccoli from your lunch.
The last piece.
And now you're angry.
But don't worry.
I got you a new thing of broccoli!
You shoulda told me that you liked it so much
before I shoved it in my mouth!
But we can put all that behind us, now, 'cause you've got
a new broccoli! So, there we go. Problem solved!
Anyway, my old man flipped the channel
just as fast as he could.
It's not about the broccoli then.
Maybe the cauliflower?
Probably not.
I've done so many potentially offensive things,
I don't even know which one she'd be mad at me for!
Although, there is one thing that does stand out.
I'll have to bite the bullet and apologize.
I don't want her to stay mad at me forever!
Okay!
Hey, Mai! Listen!
Sorry for eating your main dish!
And for stealing your apple bunny!
And your rice!
And for leaving the beans!
Oh, come on!
Why are you so mad at me?
That's all I can think of!
If it's not your lunch, then what is it?
Maybe it's because of what happened that one time!
When that Buddha statue was on your desk.
Is it because I accidently snapped its head off?
Or that I took it home and did a crappy job at fixing it?
U-Uh!
Was it because I buried it and had a secret funeral?
Or because I changed my mind, dug it back up,
and left a memorial on your desk?
Or because I changed my mind again
and decided to cremate it instead?
Well?
Help me out! I'm dying here!
Ah. Okay, so you were just listening to music
this whole time.
You couldn't hear anything, could you?
It's no problem, since I really was just talking
to myself anyway, so you didn't really miss much!
Man, that was a close one.
I almost spilled every bean I had to her.
--That last part. --Huh?
Buddha.
I didn't know.
Excuse me, Tanaka?
I'm sorry, but do you have a moment?
Well. Uh.
I just wanted to say that...
It's about your hair.
Don't you think it's getting a little big these days?
You know what?
Yes?
How 'bout a pancake?
Ah, crap!
I totally forgot I had to do this worksheet!
But I still have five minutes until class starts.
Mio already let me copy her work yesterday.
I'm begging you!
I can't ask her again!
That means, I have no choice.
Hey, uh, Mai?
So, this is totally embarrassing.
But I kinda, sorta,
completely forgot to do today's math homework.
Do you think it'd be possible if
I could take the quickest little
peek at yours before class starts?
Kay.
Oh, wow, really? Thanks!
Just gimme one sec! I'll have it copied in no time!
This sucks! I'm so late!
This sucks! This sucks!
Don't make such a racket in the morning, Masao!
This sucks!
I'm so frickin' late!
Oh, yeah? Well, I just got laid off!
Well, isn't that something.
Sorry Mai, but I think you might have given me
the wrong paper by mistake, because...
I'll buy you some juice!
Here.
Thanks so much!
I'm so late for school!
My dad just got laid off! It sucks for both of us!
Wait! The heck is that?!
Look behind you, Masao!
You've got way bigger problems now!
What are you gonna do?
Uh. I mean...
I've got bigger problems!
Why am I getting caught up in this weirdo comic?!
I can't get distracted!
I'll throw in an extra snack if you help me!
Here.
You're the best! All right, yeah, cool.
That's what I'm talkin' about. I knew you had it in you.
You didn't have to mess with me like that, you big tease!
Anyway, time to knock this thing out!
I don't even have today's worksheet. Oh, well.
I want to go to New Orleans.
So. Anyone know the solution?
Not a single person?
Mr. Akagi's class is the worst thing ever.
You get bonked on the head if you forget your homework,
and get yelled at for answering a question wrong.
Remember that a lack of in-class participation
will negatively affect your grade.
So that's how he's gonna play it.
Well, it'll take more than that to trap me, sir!
Now, what to do?
I guess since today is the 23rd, let's go with
the student assigned to seat number 23.
Not me!
Nakanojou!
Huh, he's absent?
What?!
Ohh! An arm cramp!
Of all times to be stuck like this.
Oh no, he might actually call on
me now that I can't back down.
I've gotta hide in the blind spot of his laser eyes.
Just gonna--
I'll pretend it was the chair!
Give it a little scoot.
Hey! I think maybe somebody's phone was just ringing.
Vibrate only!
Let's just hope that they have a "smart phone."
Get it?
Looks like you kids are in a great mood for math!
Right?
Uh, so, anyway, moving on.
Miss Aioi.
♪ First comes a rock, what's it gonna be? ♪
♪ Rock-paper-scissors and a one, two, three! ♪
Ready!
And lift off!
Woosh!
Why though?
Okay. I already bought sugar and milk,
so I can mark those off the list.
But I feel like I'm forgetting something important.
Did you see that insane sale on eggs today?
Yeah, I don't have that much room in my fridge, but...
Wait that's right! There was a special on eggs
at the store, and the sale ends today!
Mm... Do I have enough time?
If I hurry back now, I think I can make it.
Huh?
Aww!
A little black kitty cat!
Aww! You're just the cutest!
Uh! Hold on.
We can't adopt a cat right now.
I already have my hands full with Hakase.
Sorry, kitty.
I'm back from the grocery store.
Hiya Nano.
Huh?! It's that cat!
I captured the beast!
You can't bring in cats that you find on the street.
What? But he's so cute.
You do have a point.
But he still can't stay here!
Come on! Don't you think he's cute?
Well, I guess I do. But it's not about his cuteness.
It's just that, taking care of an animal can be
a big responsibility. So...
Can you handle it, Hakase?
I can!
Even though you won't be getting any assistance from me?
That means you're the one who has to clean his litter box.
You're not gonna help with anything?
Fine! Then you're not allowed to pet him ever!
That's not fair!
All right, maybe I can help... just a little bit.
Hakase! He's napping on my lap!
I'm gonna pet him now!
He's so fluffy!
Huh? Don't hog him!
I want to pet him, too!
His belly is so fluffy!
And his sides are super fluffy too!
His right paw is extra fluffy!
And his left paw is super fluffy too!
His little tail is the fluffiest!
His tail isn't as fluffy as this spot behind his ears.
Huh? But I think it's probably
one of the fluffiest features he has.
You're wrong! His tail isn't fluffy at all!
What's the matter?
You aren't hurt anywhere, are you?
Eureka!
Hold on a second!
Hakase?
Hey, Nano! Check it out!
I made a scarf that'll let him talk!
What an amazing invention!
Now, let's have Sakamoto try it out.
Sakamoto?
You decided to call the cat Sakamoto?
Yup! 'Cause it's the name that's on his box.
I guess that's the simplest way to go about it.
Okay! All done!
You think he's really gonna talk?
He'll talk, all right.
Here it comes.
I don't care who you think you are,
that petting was excessive.
Huh?
Also, it's common knowledge
that a cat meows when it's hungry.
Not that it matters, since I can spell it out for you now.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't aware of that.
And then there's you!
Taking the name straight from the side of the box?
Have some imagination.
I'm so sorry.
I told you the same thing, so I agree with him.
Yeah, but!
How old are you two anyway?
Eight years old.
I'm one year old.
In your human years, I'd be 20 years old.
It's Mr. Sakamoto. Capiche?
Capiche...?
While I do appreciate the free room and board,
there needs to be some ground rules.
And you'll respect those rules
since I'm the oldest one here.
Another thing you should know about cats...
Just because we're fluffy,
doesn't mean we can be pet indiscriminately.
Umm...
To be honest with you, I enjoy being pet.
But there's a limit.
You understand? Life is all about moderation.
I'll go put him back where you found him.
'Kay...
Huh?
My humblest apologies.
Hm?
Helvetica Standard.
Here you are!
Really?
But I'm late on my rent payment again this month.
And you're still okay with giving me free food?
It's fine, I'll always here to help someone in need.
If there's anything else I can
do, feel free to let me know.
Do you mean it? Well then, uh...
How about some money?
For the rent.
Don't think that I'm going to let a greedy goblin
take advantage of my kindness.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Now. Vice-Principal.
Is this...?
What, is something the matter, Principal?
You're sweating.
Why don't you go ahead and look inside the doll's body?
If I win this thing, I don't owe you the extra snacks
from any of our previous deals.
Got it?
Yeah.
I'm totally gonna win!
The battle for snacks and juice begins!
Ready... Go!
It's okay, Mai!
You were a little early on the start.
Isn't that right, Mio?
I suppose it's possible she jumped the gun. Just a tad.
See? It's fine. We can start over!
Arm wrestlers, take your positions.
Ready... Go!
And Mai is the winner!
Huh?
You caught me off guard!
I'll admit, I might have underestimated you.
But now I'm all warmed up and ready to go for real.
All right, bring it on!
Man, I didn't think my arm would still be this sore!
It's from my all-nighter!
But I'm just gonna shake it off
and get my head in the game.
'Bout time I got serious. Think you can handle me?
Ah, dang it! I completely spaced on that one!
I can't believe I threw three rounds in a row!
I never woulda seen that coming!
That's quite the surprise!
Okay. That's enough.
Hold on. Just you wait and see.
Mm-hm, I get it. I understand what happened now.
Of course! It's simple!
You're all out of beginner's luck,
and now it's the end for you! Prepare to meet your doom!
Ready!
Well, isn't this an interesting turn of events?
What do they call you again?
--Hey now. --The immoveable object, right?
Mio, hold this for me!
'Cause I'm about to unleash the unstoppable force.
Prepare for something really special!
Would you please cut that out?!
It's because you're not even trying!
I can't fight for real if you don't take this seriously!
Come at me with everything you've got this time!
I'll unleash my ultimate moves!
Earth Destroyer!
Shooting Star!
Death!
Why? I don't get it.
Why does it have to be this way?
It's only arm wrestling.
How can you be so freakin' good at it?
I completely forgot I had to pee this entire time.
I'll be right back.
I knew something was throwing
me off from the very beginning.
Yuuko?
One extra snack from the station.
And 23 juices.
My stupid arm cramp got me caught and yelled at
for not doing my homework. Today really is the worst.
More importantly, tell me!
I need to know what happens to Masao!
Come on, Mai!
Okay fine, I'll buy you another juice
if you show me what happens next.
--Here. --Yoink.
I don't know what I expected.
What was that natto doing inside of me anyway?
Was that supposed to be some kind of joke?
Well, if it was, it was "natto" very funny!
Really, that's the last "straw."
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 4.
Look forward to it!