Oh, yeah, don't worry.
It's cool. See you!
Hey, Mai, do you wanna walk home together?
Can we stop by the fire station?
Stop by what?
Why would a pair of ordinary high school girls go there?
I know what we can do!
How 'bout we go and visit
that Daiku Coffee place on the way home.
But their sizing system is kinda weird,
so don't feel too bad if you get confused
by the names and stuff.
Got 'em.
I've been there before, so I can help walk you through it.
Mai. Something's... afoot.
I'm stepping up my game.
Uh, yeah, I can see that! I just can't understand why!
Is this some sort of fashion statement or what?
It's just a joke.
She really threw me for a loop there.
It's happened. Mai's completely lost her mind.
I don't even know what to say anymore!
Oh, well. I'll just see what happens, I guess.
I wonder... What I should make for dinner tonight?
Green onions are on sale today,
so maybe I can do something with those.
Wait, no. Hakase hates onions.
Nano! Nano! Nano!
Hey. Look. I caught this crow outside.
Caught a what?
Wait! You can't bring that in here!
It's dangerous, and it might carry diseases or something!
Nah. It's fine.
Oh, I have an idea.
It's not in here.
I might die in here.
It's not in here either.
How could I have misplaced my scarf?
Greetings. I am Crow.
Pleased to make your acquaintance.
Say what?!
I'm so surprised by how polite and considerate he is.
Well, yeah, he's a crow.
You are too kind. It is an honor.
Do you think crows can drink strawberry juice?
Huh. Good question.
We should try giving him some! It'll be neat!
Oh, wow.
He's nice enough to kill bugs for us!
It was nothing. I simply did what I felt was right.
What a good crow.
Oh, hey.
What happened to that scarf you always wear, Sakamoto?
You're so silly!
We can't understand you and your cat speak!
Allow me to translate.
Ah, yes. I see.
It appears he's upset because
he would like to wear my scarf.
Ah, I see.
It's my scarf in the first place!
Hakase, did you take your scarf invention
from Sakamoto and put it on the nice crow?
This is quite a predicament.
Did you stop to think about how
that might make Sakamoto feel?
I know! I'll make him something!
Excellent idea.
It's done!
This is Biscuit #1!
You are not helping!
I must inquire.
What exactly is this "Biscuit #1" of yours capable of?
I'm very glad you inquired, Crow.
He comes with a rocket punch feature!
Here, I'll show you!
Three, two, one. Blast off!
Hang on. Shouldn't we be helping Sakamoto?
What about his scarf?
Sure, but check this out.
Let's see what power the left hand is packin'!
Three, two, one! And launch!
I'll kill you. I'll kill you all.
Well. Ha. This day has been quite entertaining.
But I believe my mischief has overstayed its welcome.
It is about time that this scarf was returned
to its rightful owner.
Though it was short-lived,
I enjoyed being able to communicate with you humans.
Mr. Crow.
You should stay with us!
Wait!
I hope for our paths to cross again one day!
Until then, I bid you farewell.
See you again!
Goodbye, Mr. Crow!
Crow.
He took my freakin' scarf!
There's no way, Chief. It's impossible.
No, trust me on this. Everything will be fine.
Yeah, but--
But what? You don't believe in me?
Of course not! I just, uh...
Chief. You can always count on me to have your back!
Perfect. Then allow me to have yours as well.
Huh? Wait!
Well? How does it feel?
Come on, use your words.
Yesterday, I dug a few pitfalls behind the gym
and filled them with a powerful adhesive.
And with this letter,
I shall lure her in to my scientifically crafted trap!
Prepare yourself, Nano Shinonome.
Today is the day.
She's here!
Gotcha!
Fascinating.
Who would've thought that Ms. Sakurai
had a little brother at this school.
Maybe I could find out more about her
through this brother of hers.
This kid. He can play Go+Soccer?!
Interesting.
'Scuse me, young man.
Yeah?
I was wondering: You don't happen to have
a boyfriend, do you?
You idiot! What is wrong with me?
Why am I like this? Why am I so stupid?
A boyfriend? No, I don't, but...
No, I don't, but...
Sprout. Sprout. Sprouting!
Wait! No, it's not! Nothing's sprouting at all!
Uh...
Sorry about that!
Just, uh, forget about what I said. Ha-ha.
Anyway, I see that you, uh, know how to play Go+Soccer?
Yeah, and I'm pretty good, too.
By the way, Mr. Takasaki.
You have a crush on my big sister, don't you?
Uh.
What?! Don't be ridiculous!
I'm just making small talk
with a fellow Go+Soccer player, that's all!
Hold on. You know how to play Go+Soccer, too?
Oh, yeah!
You're looking at the former high school MVP right here!
You know, the Go+Soccer club at this school
doesn't actually have an advisor yet.
I'll tell you what-- sign on as our club advisor
and I'll see if I can help you score some points
with my sister.
No, what makes you think that I would ever care
about something like that?
If you don't do it, then I'll tell everybody in school
that you have a thing for her,
and it'll get real awkward for you.
Uh! Blackmail?
How 'bout it? Sounds like a good deal to me.
Well.
What's it gonna be?
It's just, being a club advisor, it's kind of a hassle.
Hey, everyone!
You'll never believe what I found out!
He's doing it? I have to stop him!
There you are!
Nakanojou fell into a hole filled with glue behind the gym
and now he can't get out!
Wha--?!
We need your help, like, right now!
Hey! Who wants to hear some dirt on Mr. Takasaki?
Sir!
All right, then. Listen closely.
Okay.
Nakanojou...
...is totally okay!
Wha--?!
Maybe he's pretending to be a golf ball!
So is that why somebody shaved all of his hair off, then?
Wha--?! Draw it in.
Wha--?! I can try.
Wha--?! Hang on!
Wha--?!
First help me with this!
He likes green tea.
Stopping a student from blabbing about
a teacher's private life is just as important
as a student that needs to be excavated!
Because, well, I'm a teacher!
Mr. Takasaki!
What?!
I kept my mouth shut!
I'll be waiting for you, club advisor.
That's a good call, my dude.
Annaka, let's bounce!
'Kay!
There's no time to waste.
After all, I'm a teacher!
It's this way!
One sec.
Even though I always thought his hair was weird,
I do feel kinda bad for shaving it off.
So...
I guess I should dig him out.
He doesn't know I set the trap in the first place,
so it should be fine.
What's this? What's going on?
Where am I?
This feels weird! I don't like it! I'm stuck!
Anyone? Uh. Please?
My hair.
Run away!
My hair!
♪ Swim, swim! ♪
♪ Shark, shark, chomp! ♪
♪ That is what a shark does best! ♪
"The Life of Chitchi." Check her out!
What the heck?!
Help me!
What the heck?
My hair!
--What the heck? --Help me!
What happened here?
--Help me! --My hair.
--Help me! --What the what?
Oh, my. That was a close one.
What's with the hole? That's just dangerous.
--Help me! --My hair.
I'm heading out!
This is it.
I won't call out Mai's jokes today!
It's like she's practically begging me
to make jabs at her.
She just lobs 'em up, and I can't stop myself
from knocking 'em out of the park!
But if I don't cut it out now,
we're gonna get stuck in some
weird, never-ending joke cycle!
We're just normal high school girls
living our ordinary high school lives.
At least we're supposed to be.
But the way we act is anything but ordinary.
But starting today, that's all gonna change.
My resolve is like a diamond,
and this diamond is unbreakable!
Hey. Good morning, Yuuko.
Hey! How's it going?
Double glasses!
This is harder than I thought!
She really brought her A game today!
It's almost like she's testing me!
But I won't give in!
I can--no, I will change!
Hello, Mai! Selamat pagi !
Perfect.
And now's my chance to start an ordinary conversation.
Oh, yeah, I was wondering:
Did you see yesterday's Muscle Theater show?
Wha--? Wait, am I supposed to choose?
Where are my glasses?
It's just one gag after another with her today!
And the more I ignore them, the more she does it!
But I can't give in! I have to stay strong!
Don't take the bait!
What's up with you, Mai?
You've got two pairs of glasses on!
How dare you, Tanaka! I wanted to call her out!
The one thing in this world that I wanted
and you took it away from me!
Ah! Wait! No, this is a good thing!
It might just help me not make fun of her!
Wait, hold on.
What class do we have for first period today?
No idea!
But did you hear that Ms. Nakamura tripped
and fell the other day?
No. I hope she's okay.
Wait, hold on.
What class do we have for first period today?
Uh, didn't you just ask--?
Shut your mouth, me!
That was so sneaky, I almost didn't notice!
She's changing up her tactics
to try and catch me off guard!
Crafty, Mai. Very crafty.
All right, who's on day duty today?
Stand. Bow.
Take your sheet.
Okay, let's get started with class. Everyone...
"Take your sheet"?
Are you freaking kidding me with this?
And nobody even called her out on it!
Now then, who would like to read this section?
Me.
Of course she would!
Sure, now go ahead.
Right.
"A peaceful shade enveloped the mountain"...
She's reading it!
She's saying the words!
"It was my first time there"...
She's saying them perfectly.
Which means... that she...
She memorized it!
You know what?
Calling someone out...
...it feels...
...so darn good!
I apologize for shouting randomly.
I'll be in the hallway.
Oh. Okay.
So... this is how it is.
Maybe things don't have to change.
Because...
This is the path that we chose together.
Yuuko.
This entire time...
...I had contacts on.
Very well played, my friend!
Hm?
Wake up, Hakase. You shouldn't sleep here.
You should crawl into bed or you might catch a cold, okay?
Are you listening to me?
Gimme a little longer.
Huh? Longer for what?
That's what!
Sakamoto, you should really go to your bed, too, y'know.
Uh. Sure.
In the end, she had to be carried.
I'm the three of spades!
My number may be low, but don't count me out!
The deck may be stacked against me, too,
but that's not a deal breaker!
This spade is my strong suit, after all!
The next episode of My Ordinary Life is Episode 18!
Look forward to it!