¶¶
( explosions )
( Explosions continue )
( Woman vocalizing )
Alien:
T-this can't be happening!
Even the mighty groribas,
the best warrior we had,
was defeated?!
What manner of creature is he?
And how'd he get aboard our ship
in the first place?
Damn it! Melzargard was
supposed to be guarding
this ship against any threats!
Now he and I are
the only elite fighters left
to fend off
this barbaric biped!
( Operators chatter )
( Fighter sighs )
I bet he's just mucking about!
I need him now.
Curse the bastard!
Leader: Geryuganshoop,
what is the problem?
Geryuganshoop:
Lord boros, I'm sorry.
I've made a terrible mistake.
I've allowed one
of the natives of this planet
to infiltrate the ship.
In the mere four minutes
since he came aboard,
23% of the ship
has been damaged.
It seems he is alone,
but has somehow managed
to instantly kill
every warrior
sent to intercept him.
I'm at a loss here.
Lord boros: Do not panic.
As long as the power sphere
remains intact,
the ship
will continue to function.
The damage thus far
seems to be limited
to the crew's living quarters,
but our pawns alone
won't be enough.
Geryuganshoop,
my top lieutenants--
you, groribas, and melzargard--
will destroy him.
Show him what we're made of.
Geryuganshoop: Uh...
Groribas has unfortunately
just fallen, sir.
Lord boros: He what?
Geryuganshoop: But let me
get melzargard back here.
The two of us working together
will wipe out the intruder
without fail, I assure you!
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
Anchor: Our top story--
over city a,
an enormous object
has suddenly appeared
and is hovering in the sky.
We now go live at the scene.
Reporter: Reporting for news 4.
The city's on high alert.
All the main roads leading in
to city a have been closed off,
and officials
are keeping a watchful eye.
According to survivors,
city a has been almost
entirely demolished
and lays in ruin.
( Helicopter thrumming )
Reporter #2: This image
of the giant flying object
was captured
with a telephoto lens.
We have a local expert here
to comment on the situation.
Expert: Most likely,
this is the act
of an extraterrestrial being,
or it's an unidentified
life-form that has
a highly advanced civilization
unbeknownst to us.
Of course,
these are all hypotheses.
Other possibilities
exist as well.
Reporter #2: I see.
Reporter #3: There have
also been eyewitness accounts
of very powerful life-forms
descending to the ground
from what is considered
to be the spacecraft.
Several class-s heroes
are presently at the location
tackling the issue.
We'll keep you updated
as more information develops.
( Puri-puri prisoner panting )
Iairon: He pummeled that thing
with nothing but the power
of his bare fists.
That's a class-s hero for you.
Even so...
( Puri-puri prisoner grunts )
Iairon: That won't do any good!
It possesses
incredible regenerative powers.
And be sure not to let it
hit any part of you.
A single blow instantly
tore my entire arm off.
( Melzargard chuckles )
Iairon: Dodge its attacks
at all costs!
Bang: Let me give it a try.
( Melzargard grunts )
Should we use a bombardment
to finish off these humans?
Head #4: Yes, that is good.
Head #1: Contact the ship.
Head #4: I will go.
( Chuckles )
Metal bat: Get back here!
- ( Head #4 grunts )
- Metal bat: Scummy bat!
You'd better mind your manners!
I hope you like mincemeat,
freak!
Geryuganshoop: Melzargard!
What are you doing?
Melzargard: I'm in battle.
Geryuganshoop: Intruder here!
Melzargard: Ridiculous.
Geryuganshoop: It's true! Hurry!
Finish them off,
and get up here immediately!
Saitama: Crap,
this one's locked, too.
Hey, open the door!
You've got a visitor!
Oops. Think I broke it.
Metal bat: Huh?
Head #4: I know.
I'll rip your limbs off,
then make you the ship mascot.
That is good.
( Metal bat gasps, spits )
Put yourself
together again, huh?
( Yells )
I'm gonna keep you
for batting practice!
( Bang grunts )
( Melzargard yells )
¶¶
Iairon: Comrades!
Direct physical attacks
have no effect on it!
All of our efforts
have only been in vain!
Let's withdraw for now.
There must be some other way
we can destroy it,
like using heat.
Metal bat: Smashing is
all I'm good at! Forget it!
Bang: This is all I know
how to do as well.
Can't teach an old dog
new tricks. My apologies.
Puri-puri prisoner:
That goes for me, too.
Sorry, sweet iairon.
Atomic samurai:
Iai, I'm disappointed.
Don't you have faith in me?
There's nothing I can't cut.
Iairon: It's pointless.
These guys are used
to coming out on top.
They aren't the type to listen.
Geryuganshoop: Melzargard!
Look, I really need you
on the ship.
Getting rid of the intruder
takes priority!
Melzargard: I'd love to,
but I'm still busy down here.
These creatures are persistent.
Geryuganshoop:
You've gotta be kidding.
The life-forms down there are
proving tough to handle, too?
What the hell's with this place?
Melzargard:
Nothing tough about them.
What's the ship's status?
Is it going down or what?
Geryuganshoop:
It's not going down,
but more than half the crew
have already been killed
by this intruder.
Melzargard: There's no way!
I need to end this fast, then.
Begin cleansing my location with
a bombardment from the ship.
Geryuganshoop: Like I said, I've
got my hands full right now.
Besides, artillery bombardment's
the job of the lower ranks.
Melzargard: Well,
I'm in a situation
where I can't return onboard.
Geryuganshoop: All right, fine.
I'll notify the artillery crews
of your predicament.
Don't get caught up
in the barrage
and die, understood?!
Melzargard: Wait!
Hold on a second!
You should come down here
and help me.
That'd be
a much faster solution.
Hey! Geryuganshoop!
Damn him.
Just how tough is this intruder?
Metal bat: How about
another one?!
¶¶
head #4: More attacks?
Keep trying.
It is good that you're
exhausting yourself.
Metal bat: Hmm?
What the hell is this?
( Head #4 gasps )
Metal bat: A marble?
Why have you got one of these?
Head #4: G-give it back!
Metal bat: Here you go.
Head #4: Yaah!
Metal bat: Whoa!
Damn! That's nasty,
you nasty bastard.
Are you dead?
Hey! I just
discovered somethin'!
These guys have
a marble-thing inside 'em!
Destroy it, and they die!
( Melzargard gasps )
Bang: Oh!
Atomic samurai:
Yeah, nice work!
So I just
have to slice away at you
until I hit this vital marble
he's talking about!
¶¶
melzargard: Impossible.
I've been growing that head
for a hundred years,
and it got killed in this dump?
Either way, you scum
are dead when the shells hit.
They're coming,
and there's nothing
you can do to stop them.
( Alarm blaring )
Geryuganshoop:
A-attention, intruder!
Cease your destructive acts,
and depart from this vessel
immediately!
This is your only warning.
Leave at once!
- I-If you do not comply...
- Saitama: Hmm?
Geryuganshoop:
We'll have no choice
but to unleash
all our forces against you!
Saitama: That's kinda weird.
I'm hearing a voice
from inside my head.
Geryuganshoop:
Take one more step,
and you're dead!
Eh, we'll show no mercy!
Saitama: Even if
I wanted to leave,
I'm lost, and I can't
find my way out of here!
Geryuganshoop:
Really? You'd leave?
Okay. Then I will guide you.
Take a right.
Then go up the stairs.
Wait there
for further instruction.
Saitama: A right?
Geryuganshoop:
E-exactly, a right.
( Saitama chuckles )
I guess I'll go left then.
Geryuganshoop: No, wait!
Not that way! Eh,
w-wait a second! Hang on!
Didn't you hear me? That's not--
you ca--
all right, that was my fault.
Poor directions.
Uh, I'll come to you.
Please, just stay right there!
( Stammers ) No!
( Operators stammer )
Saitama: Now, this place
looks like a control room
or something.
Geryuganshoop: You...
Saitama: Hmm?
An octopus?
Huh?
Geryuganshoop: You dare
enter this place uninvited
and bust up our ship?
Saitama: Hey! What the?
The debris is flying at me.
Geryuganshoop:
Now geryuganshoop,
the supreme telekinetic power
in the universe,
will grind you
into blood sausage!
( Panel beeping )
Gunner: Good. Just about there.
Okay, my lord!
Bombardment preparations
are nearly complete.
Shall I proceed as ordered?
Maybe he went to the bathroom.
Well, when you gotta go,
you gotta go.
( Geryuganshoop gasps )
Gunner: Hey, lord geryuganshoop!
Saitama: Telekinetic?
Like psychic powers?
Geryuganshoop:
You leave me no choice, worm.
Telekinetic gravitational wave!
( Operators shriek )
Geryuganshoop: Die, earthling!
¶¶
( crew gasp, scream )
Geryuganshoop:
There's nowhere to run.
My unparalleled
telekinetic powers
allow me to manipulate
the forces of gravity!
Do you know
what a black hole is, you ape?
Inside one, the gravitational
effects are so strong,
even light itself cannot escape!
What the...
Saitama: Hmm?
( Geryuganshoop sighs )
( Grunts )
Saitama: Eh,
now what are you doing?
Geryuganshoop: Take this!
Telekinetic shower of rubble!
¶¶
( Laughs ) There.
I got him that time!
( Gasps )
Saitama: Psychic powers?
Too bad you're just wasting 'em.
All you're doin'
is tossing pebbles around.
You don't really need powers
to do that.
Geryuganshoop: How could...
I, geryuganshoop--
impossible.
Saitama: Excuse me.
( Aliens gasp, stammer )
Saitama: I've got
a question for you.
Mind telling me
where your boss is?
Both: Eh?
( Beeping )
Child emperor: This isn't good.
Genos: Hmm?
Supervisor: Has that
been confirmed?
Sitch: Yes, I'm afraid so.
Child emperor said
that the energy level
in the spaceship
is rising
at an incredibly rapid rate.
Supervisor: What should we do
about the civilians?
Sitch: Recall the search
and rescue teams for now.
Have everyone find shelter
and take cover.
You'll be
under serious fire soon.
( Supervisor gasps )
¶¶
( man panting )
Mumen rider: Hop on!
( Beeping )
Gunner: There we go.
Geryuganshoop still
hasn't gotten back to me,
but whatever.
Let's see.
From what I recall,
the order
was to concentrate fire
around the enemies
on the surface
who are fighting melzargard.
( Puri-puri prisoner grunts )
( Head groans )
Metal bat: Only two heads left.
I'll bust
those suckers wide open!
Head #1: Is it time yet?
Head #5:
Ship bombardment coming.
Quite soon.
( Panel beeping )
Gunner: Oh. There they are.
All right. Bye-bye, problems.
( All gasp )
Head #1: It's over.
Head #5: You will die.
There's no escape.
¶¶
Gunner: What the?
What happened?
Bang: How did...
Puri-puri prisoner:
They just stopped. ( Gasps )
Tornado: All of you muscle-heads
would be dead without me.
Can't you finish one small fry?
Maybe you should try
starting over from class c.
Hey, aliens,
take your shells back.
¶¶
sitch: Incredible!
( Worker gasps )
Gunner: I wanna go home.
( Overlapping chatter )
Man: Come on.
Man #2: All right, son.
Supervisor: I had no idea
you were here.
Thanks a lot, mumen rider.
Mumen rider: I'm sure
there are more survivors.
Where should I look?
Narrowing the search area
will save lives.
Supervisor:
I'm not sure if you--
mumen rider: I'm ready.
I'll go rescue them right now.
Stinger: Sounds like a plan.
- We want to know, too.
- Lightning Max: Yeah.
Can't let this guy
hog the limelight.
Supervisor: It's stinger
and lightning Max.
Stinger: So, uh,
can we borrow this?
Supervisor: You guys...
( Melzargard yells )
¶¶
Bang: Nice catch.
I found it.
Begone.
( Head #5 gasps )
Bang: Only one left.
Atomic samurai:
They got silverfang!
Iairon: No. A direct hit.
( Melzargard laughs )
Weak. Weak!
You are all so very weak.
Dead after a single hit.
( Metal bat scoffs )
Melzargard: A change of tactics
was all I needed.
If I forget about defense
and focus on my attacks,
this will all be over quickly.
You're next, swordsman! Hah!
I will spring past that blade
and squeeze your skull
'til it pops!
Atomic samurai: If you think
you can do it, then be my guest.
Lord boros: He's come.
¶¶
the finest warrior
this planet has to offer.
I can sense no limit
to his energy.
Saitama: Are you the boss man
of these invaders?
Lord boros: Wonderful!
Saitama: Huh?
Lord boros: Before we fight,
let us exchange names.
I lead the pirate band
known as dark matter,
and I am the dominator
of the universe.
My name is boros.
Saitama: I'm a hero for fun.
I mean, a--a real
professional hero,
and my name is saitama.
Lord boros: Saitama.
Saitama: Look, dude,
I don't know
what the denominator
of the universe
wants with earth,
but you sure did make
a big mess out of city a.
Lord boros:
What I want with earth?
There exists a prophecy.
Saitama: Prophecy?
What do you mean?
Lord boros:
I was once a traveler,
exploring the universe,
ravaging everything in sight.
But I was too strong.
Eventually, I found there were
none left who could face me.
I came to know the torment
of utter,
all-encompassing boredom.
Then one day,
a great seer told me,
somewhere on a faraway planet,
a being exists who is my match,
one who could rekindle
my passion for battle.
That was nearly 20 years ago.
Have you any concept
of the distance
I've traveled to get here?
My men thought
the prophecy was a ruse,
a fairy tale made up
to focus my attention
and lure me away,
but now I'm certain it was true.
Come, and give stimulation
to my existence.
That is why I am here!
¶¶
saitama: Are you an idiot?
You can't just go around
attacking other planets
simply to liven up
your boring little life.
Even telemarketers wouldn't
think of something that dumb.
Oh.
Lord boros: This set of armor,
which was used
to seal in my immeasurable,
irresistible power,
has now been broken.
Saitama: Okay.
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Lord boros grunting )
It is time!
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )