¶¶
( Man gasps )
( Man #2 gasps ) This is bad.
Astronaut: Initiating
docking procedures.
Operator: Roger.
( Astronaut gasps )
( Overlapping chatter )
Man #3: Elevating from six
to nine on the Torino scale!
( Overlapping chatter )
( Beeping )
Supervisor: So the course
suddenly shifted?
I see.
Then we'll discuss how best
to deal with the situation.
Genos: Should I go
right now, then?
Understood.
Master, for some reason,
the hero association
wants me to come in.
I will be back later.
Saitama: Okay.
Maybe you're getting fired.
( Laughs )
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
Hero: Ah, you must be genos.
It's very nice
to make your acquaintance.
I'm bang.
( Genos thinking ) Class s,
rank 3, a.K.A. Silverfang.
He possesses true skill.
( Aloud )
The association called me in.
Bang: Everyone else
is over at headquarters.
This branch office
is empty now.
Every class-s hero
got the call to come here,
but you and I are
the only ones who showed up.
Genos: And why is that?
Bang: Maybe this branch
is too far away,
or perhaps they're busy.
Of course, some of
the more coldblooded ones
simply don't bother.
Then again,
it's hard to blame them.
We're only called
when there's an impossible
problem to take care of,
and today's dilemma
is no exception.
The threat level is dragon,
meaning it's
a worst-case scenario.
35 minutes from now,
a huge meteor
will strike city z.
They're asking
if nearby class-s heroes
can do anything about it.
( Genos gasps ) Meteor?
Bang: Apparently
it suddenly changed paths.
That new trajectory
means the end for us.
The impact
will wipe out city z.
I'm afraid there's nothing
we can do this time.
You should think about
evacuating with your loved ones,
as the others have.
Genos: Do the citizens know?
Bang: I was told
the powers-that-be
would issue evacuation orders
30 minutes before it hits.
( Siren blaring )
Announcer: Attention! This is
an important announcement
from the hero association.
( Bang chuckles )
People are surely
going to panic.
Genos: And you, old fellow?
Bang: "Old fellow," is it?
I told you. Call me bang.
Genos: You are not evacuating?
Bang: There's a dojo
for martial arts here
that's been in my family
for generations.
I cannot abandon it.
Fist of flowing water
crushing rock.
Ever heard of it?
Huh. He left.
¶¶
announcer:
Emergency evacuation warning.
- The threat level is dragon.
- ( Horns honking )
Evacuate immediately
to a safe distance.
T-minus 21 minutes
until meteor impact.
City z will be
completely destroyed.
Man: It's huge.
Man #2: No way
we can escape that thing.
Announcer: ...Leave
as quickly as possible.
Genos: So many people
have given up hope
of surviving this tragedy.
It is not just city z
that is in danger.
The neighboring cities
will also sustain damage.
It is too late to evacuate.
I did not expect
to be testing
this prototype so soon.
( Beep )
¶¶
Let me see if an attack
from my incineration Cannon
at full power
will do the trick.
Master saitama lives here, too.
I cannot possibly evacuate
without him.
What is that?
You are bofoi, correct?
Bofoi: And you are
the new boy, genos.
Have you come
to stop the meteor?
Genos: Yes.
( Thinking )
Class s, rank 7.
Uses intense firepower
to obliterate opponents
along with everything
in their vicinity.
Does he also live in city z,
or did he rush here
putting his life at risk?
Bofoi, I am in need
of your assistance.
Bofoi: I refuse.
Genos: Why is that?
Bofoi: I only answered the call
to field-test my new weapon.
The meteor is a perfect target.
Genos: A field test?
If that meteor hits,
you will die, too.
- Bofoi: Fortunately I won't.
- Genos: How so?
Bofoi: What you are talking to
is a remote-controlled drone.
I am a good distance away.
Terribly sorry
to disappoint you,
but my life's
not at stake here.
Also, I am not bofoi.
I am metal knight.
Heroes call each other
by their hero names,
not their real names.
Everyone knows that.
Looks like it's time.
Sorry to cut off
our little chat.
( Genos scoffs )
All right.
Bofoi: Launch missiles!
( Genos thinking )
Metal knight?
I cannot fire
with his missiles in the way.
Amazing.
Such destructive power.
This hero is dangerous.
I must be careful around him.
( Gasps )
Bofoi: Unfortunate.
Not quite potent enough.
¶¶
genos: 33 seconds remain
until impact.
To fire my incineration Cannon
at full power,
I need five seconds
to charge it,
but the target
is already dangerously close.
Additionally,
if I do happen to take it out,
what then?
The meteor may break apart
and still cause a disaster.
Will my weapon
be powerful enough to stop it?
Even metal knight's countless
missiles had no effect.
( Gasps )
Bang: First off, be calm.
I see you've lost composure.
Put your mind at rest.
You're far too young
to be worried about failure.
When your back's up against
the wall, you must take action.
Overthinking
won't change things.
The best course
is to muddle through.
Genos: Muddling through
is the best course?
Bang: Hmm?
Genos: He is right.
If the outcome
will not change either way,
then how can I just die
without giving it my all?
- Bang, get down!
- Bang: Ohh!
Genos: I will no longer think
about failure or repercussions.
I will just
pour everything I have...
Into one shot!
( Yells )
Damn, it is not working.
Bang: Hold on!
I think I see the meteor
being pushed back!
Genos: Really?
Bang: Nope.
It was just my imagination.
Genos: You old fool!
So this--this will be my grave.
( Groans )
( Powering down )
Only nine more seconds.
Leave now, bang,
or you will die.
Saitama: Old man,
take care of genos.
Bang: Hmm?
¶¶
w-who are you? Who sent you?
Saitama: I'm just a guy
who's a hero for the fun of it.
¶¶
Genos: Master?!
Saitama: You're not...
Gonna fall...
On my town!
Bang: He shattered it!
Unbelievable!
Oh, no.
Genos: It is falling!
Bang: It's not
just this building.
The destruction
from the splintered meteor
is spreading
throughout the entire city.
Saitama: I guess
that takes care of that.
Reporter: Although city z
was able to avoid
total destruction
from the meteor,
the city was still
relentlessly devastated,
with the destructive effects
of the giant fireball's
fragments visible everywhere.
- According to...
- Genos: Look at this.
If only the hero association
had called you to help
instead of me, master.
If you had been assigned
to work with metal knight,
all the damage caused could have
easily been minimized.
Saitama: But you said
that metal knight guy
wasn't interested
in helping at all, didn't you?
So stop worrying about it.
I think we kept the damage
to a minimum.
Since no one died,
we should just call it a win.
( Genos thinking )
He is right.
Master's punch greatly lessened
the meteor's momentum
and destructive power.
Theoretically,
the shockwaves from the meteor
would have annihilated
everything for miles around.
Stopping it
was nothing short of a miracle.
I would not be surprised
if people talk about master
for years to come,
praising him
as a man of courage.
But master himself has no idea.
Some are even making him out
to be the bad guy
for causing the partial
destruction of city z,
despite saving it as a whole.
No, I should not
mention it to him.
Saitama: By the way,
do you think what happened
moved us up in the ranking?
Genos: Yes, in fact, it did.
I progressed
from rank 17 to 16.
Metal knight moved up
from rank seven to six.
Master, you shot from class c,
rank 342, up to rank five.
Saitama: Number five?!
- From 342 to five?
- ( Birds squawking )
Whoa, what the hell?!
That's crazy!
Genos: Well, honestly,
your performance was worthy
of class a or even class s.
I mean, the threat level
to this event was dragon.
Saitama: Yeah?
Genos: If there
had been no damage,
I am sure you would be
at class s, rank 5.
Saitama: Huh?
Genos: Smashing the meteor alone
would earn a jump
from class c to class a,
but I think the hero association
must have assumed
that metal knight and I
played a big role
in the tide of events
that occurred.
Saitama: By the way,
they always report threat levels
as demon or tiger or whatever.
Does all that
really mean anything?
( Genos gasps ) It does.
Tiger--a crisis threatening
massive loss of life.
Demon--a crisis threatening
to halt the functioning
of an entire city
or its destruction.
Dragon--a crisis threatening
the destruction
of multiple cities.
God--a crisis
threatening human extinction.
Saitama: Wow. I had no idea.
Genos: I believe that heroes
normally take these
threat levels into consideration
when deciding whether or not
to respond to a call.
But I guess such things
do not matter to you.
Saitama: Well,
of course they don't.
- Genos: Hmm?
- Saitama: If heroes run away,
who's left to help?
Um, what are you doing?
Genos: I must record
your words of wisdom.
Saitama: Well, anyway,
it wasn't much
for such a huge jump
in rankings.
Right.
I'll be out for a bit.
Genos: You are
going out, master?
Hold on. I will come with you.
Saitama: You stay here.
If something heroic happens,
you'll get
all the credit again.
This place is a total wreck.
Oh.
My favorite supermarket
got smashed,
and the crappy
apartment building
I got kicked out of is...
Just fine.
Damn.
- Tank-top tiger: Hey.
- Saitama: Huh?
Tank-top tiger:
You no-good cheating bastard.
Saitama: Uh, who might you be?
( Tank-top tiger sputters )
You know damn well who I am!
Tank-top tiger!
Hey, brother!
It's that guy I told you about!
( Saitama thinking )
Seriously, who is this guy?
Hero: Did I hear you
call me, little bro?
Tank-top tiger: Brother!
Hero: The hero known
as tank-top blackhole is here!
So it's you,
the fraud who takes credit
for work done by class-s heroes
to jump the rankings!
Saitama: What the--
tank-top tiger:
Nobody could move up the ranks
to number five so quickly
without cheating, you cheater!
Saitama: Huh?
So what do you guys want?
Tank-top tiger:
What? Don't you know?
We came here to beat you up
so bad you'll never be able to--
tank-top blackhole:
Hang on, little bro.
Tank-top tiger: Hmm?
Tank-top blackhole:
That plan's not gonna work.
The bastard won't learn
from that kind of lesson.
Let's make him
really pay for this
by using
the most brutal method there is.
( Deep breath )
Was it you?!
Are you the jerk-off responsible
for destroying this city?!
Saitama: Huh?
( Tank-top tiger thinking )
I get it!
There are tons of people
in this city
who are totally pissed at him.
Tank-top blackhole:
You're unbelievable!
How can you even
show your face around here?!
Woman: Hmm?
Tank-top tiger:
Smart play, brother.
He's gonna use their anger...
Tank-top blackhole:
Do you feel nothing
at the sight
of this devastation?
( Onlookers murmuring )
Tank-top tiger: ...To completely
break his spirit.
Tank-top blackhole:
Look at you gloating,
thinking you've actually
saved these people!
Why else would you be walking
around here so shamelessly?
Thanks to your screw-up,
these citizens
have nowhere to go!
Their homes
have been destroyed!
If you were
gonna fail this hard,
why'd you even butt in?!
The other heroes would
have done a way better job
without your help!
And yet you still
wanna play hero,
even after causing
such a disaster?
Look at this place!
All this destruction
is your doing, you jerk!
Man: Yeah, that's right.
You, all this is your fault!
( Tank-top blackhole chuckles )
( Thinking )
They took the bait.
Hey, do you hear that?
The heart-wrenching cry
of someone who lost his home!
Look at them all,
victims of your
thoughtless actions!
You should
be ashamed of yourself!
Man #2: That's right!
Man #3: Yeah, you tell him!
Tank-top blackhole:
Haven't you even thought
- to take responsibility?
- Woman: Yeah, creep!
Man #4: You're inhuman!
Tank-top blackhole:
You're no hero!
Give it up!
Give it up! Give it up!
( Together )
Give it up!
Give it up! Give it up!
Crowd:
Give it up!
- Tank-top tiger: We got him.
- ( Chanting continues )
His pride should be
shattered to pieces by now.
That's what he gets
for cheating, the idiot.
( Genos gasps )
Crowd: Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up!
Tank-top tiger: So this
is mob mentality, huh?
I'd sure hate to be
on the wrong side of this.
Crowd: Give it up! Give it up!
Give it up! Give it up!
- Bang: Saitama.
- ( Chanting continues )
Without a shadow of a doubt,
you saved this city.
Yet look
how the city treats you.
Reality can be so ugly.
You're strong,
the strongest man
I've ever seen.
That's why I refrain
from saying anything.
I don't want to influence you.
I'd hate to see you rotting away
into oblivion in this industry.
Unfortunately, resigning
may be your best option.
Tank-top blackhole:
Time to finish him off!
Hey! Look, you guys!
He's getting ready to fight!
Saitama: Huh?
What are you talking--
tank-top blackhole:
No way! Seriously?!
You're gonna take out
your frustration
on these people here,
just like you
destroyed their city?!
Do you just kill
everyone you don't like?
I won't let you do that!
We, the tank-top brothers,
won't stand by
while you resort to violence!
If you're the hero
you say you are,
then fight us both
fair and square!
Bang: So they're out
to crush a rookie
and perform a publicity stunt
at the same time, are they?
( Sighs ) I'd say
they've gotten a little greedy.
No wonder they can't rise
above class b.
( Crowd murmuring, jeering )
Tank-top tiger:
I, tank-top tiger,
who fights
like a true tiger, and...
Tank-top blackhole:
Tank-top blackhole,
who can crush them all with
a grip strength of 2,800 p.S.I!
Tank-top tiger:
We will punish all who stray
from the path of a hero!
Now prepare for pain!
( Yells )
- ( Yelps )
- Tank-top blackhole: Hmm?
- ( Crash )
- Damn it!
You're dead!
( Screams )
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
I give up! I give up!
You're crushing my hand!
Saitama: Wait. Really?
You're kidding, right?
Tank-top blackhole:
Please let go!
I give up for real! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry
for lying about you!
Saitama: Nope,
you weren't lying.
I'm the one
who smashed that big meteor!
Anyone with a complaint,
let's hear it!
Speak up!
( Man #5 gasps )
Man #6: Because of what you did,
my brand-new car was--
saitama: You shut
your damn mouth!
Why would I give a crap
about how you're put out?
Tell it to the meteor,
not me, jackass!
Listen up!
I don't do this hero thing
for admiration or approval
or anything like that!
I do it because I want to,
understand?!
So if you wanna blame me,
go ahead, you baldies!
Man #7: But you're
the one who's bald.
Saitama: What did you say?!
Genos: Master.
Saitama: Oh, hey, genos.
What's going on?
Give me just a minute.
These guys are saying i'm--
genos: We must go home, master.
Saitama: Hmm?
¶¶
saitama: Oh.
You think we should?
Damn it. That guy's face
is burned into my brain.
I'll never be able
to forget him.
- Genos: Master.
- Saitama: Hmm?
Genos: Listen.
I want you to know
I have never met anyone
as amazing as you.
Saitama: What brought that on?
You're creeping me out.
Genos: Even if the public
does not appreciate you
or what you have done,
I will still follow you.
Saitama: You don't
have to butter me up like that.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
man: I hear there's
some amazing hero
in class c right now.
Man #2: Wait. Class c?
Man #3: The guy who says
he smashed the meteor, right?
Woman: That's just a rumor.
Man #4: Going after weak guys
and then
calling yourself a hero?
Man #5: Heh.
Guess it just goes to show
you can't really count
on any of 'em.