- ( Monster laughs )
- ( Footsteps rumbling )
Humans, if you wish to be spared
from annihilation, take heed!
I come bearing
a message from the depths!
( Mumen rider panting )
( Monster laughs )
You will surrender the surface
to us, the clan of the seafolk!
Thereafter, you shall
become our nourishment,
bipedal human scum!
Hmm?
What a head!
Are you related to an octopus
by any chance?
( Laughs )
- ( Crowd murmuring )
- Man: Look at this,
and I heard it was
that same guy again.
Man #2: What was his name?
Man #1: I forget,
but he's super-strong.
( Mumen rider panting )
Class c?
Never seen him before.
I've gotta keep up.
¶¶
( Singer vocalizing )
( Woman screams )
Help, somebody!
( Man screams )
Monster: We,
the clan of seafolk,
now rule the surface, humans!
It is useless to resist!
( Man yells )
Monster: Eh?
You'll pay for that, human!
Hero: Don't worry.
The class-a hero stinger
is here!
I'm just 11th
and rising in the rankings,
but I'm the first one
here to help.
At your service, everyone!
Man #2: Yes! It's stinger!
Man #3: We're saved for sure!
Woman #2: Show 'em who's boss!
( Monsters growling )
Stinger: Listen up, fish!
Anyone who needs a new blowhole
drilled into their torso,
step right on up!
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )
Genos: Master,
it seems you have moved up
to rank two in class c.
You are close
to entering into class b.
Saitama: Class b, huh?
So that means
I won't have any more
weekly hero quotas, right?
- Genos: Correct.
- ( Telephone rings )
Oh, excuse me.
Hello. City j?
It is a bit far.
Are there no other
competent heroes nearby?
Saitama: That's one busy guy.
Genos: Master.
The aggressive monster
you defeated
on your way home the other day,
it called itself
one of the seafolk, right?
- Saitama: I don't remember.
- ( Genos gasps )
Reporter: Several monsters
calling themselves
the clan of the seafolk
have appeared in city j
and are attacking...
Genos: There is a class-a hero
fighting them
who is all alone
and on the brink of defeat.
Reporter: ...But the media
believes he is at his limit.
His extreme fatigue and pain
are apparent.
A response
from the hero association
is desperately needed.
Mumen rider: Hang on, buddy!
Reporter:
The threat level is tiger.
All citizens should stay out of
the area for their own safety.
( Stinger chuckles )
I gotta say, you've got spunk,
you slimy bastards.
My beloved bamboo shoot here
is stoked to battle enemies
with some grit for a change,
but I'm afraid
it's time to end this.
Monster #2:
Quit your boasting, human!
Your ridiculous fan club
ran off long ago.
Monster #3:
Your death will be painful.
For the taking of our brothers'
lives, you will suffer.
Stinger: Four fish to go.
It's actually a lot easier...
Without an audience!
Sing, bamboo shoot!
( Monsters yelling )
Stinger: Gigantic drill stinger,
quadruple thrust!
I did it.
I beat those bastards!
These monsters were
probably a god-level threat,
and I defeated them
all by myse--
deep sea king: You know...
When something's so annoying,
watching it die is a pleasure.
( Thunder crashes )
Saitama: How much farther is it
to city j?
Genos: We are almost there,
but I am not getting
any readings.
I will scout ahead.
Once their location
is confirmed,
I will let you know.
Saitama: Oh. Hey!
- ( Siren blaring )
- Hmm?
Announcer:
This is an announcement
from the hero association.
The threat level is tiger,
tiger.
All citizens,
please stay clear of the area.
Supervisor:
Was the warning issued?
Woman: The request
just went out, sir.
Man: Good. But now it's looking
like we're gonna need
to update the announcement.
- Woman: Huh?
- Supervisor: What do you mean?
Man: Stinger is down, sir.
( Supervisor gasps )
Mumen rider: Mumen rider here.
I'm heading in now.
Give me the location.
Operator: We're sorry.
All lines are busy at this time.
Mumen rider: Where are they?
Hero: Hey, best forget about it!
Class-c heroes
can't handle this one.
Mumen rider: Huh?
Hero #2: It's true.
The word just came down.
Announcer:
Emergency evacuation warning.
The threat level has been raised
from tiger to demon.
- All residents...
- Hero #1: See what I mean?
Announcer:
...Please evacuate immediately.
Hero #1: Hey!
Announcer: I repeat,
all residents of city j,
please evacuate immediately.
Deep sea king: Evacuate?
The fools.
As if I'd let even one
of these apes escape.
¶¶
hero #3: I see.
So that's the one
that got stinger,
but he's the last of 'em.
Should I wait for backup?
If it's one-on-one,
maybe I can--
( deep sea king chuckles )
( Hero #3 yelling, babbling )
Deep sea king:
That stings a little.
Why would you do this?
Hero #3: Damn it.
How'd he get behind me?
I was so surprised,
my voice went crazy.
Plus, my gunpowder-charged
lightning kick had zero effect!
I can't win.
Deep sea king:
And who might you be?
Hero #3: I am...
The hero called lightning Max.
Fight me!
Deep sea king: Fight you?
Lightning Max:
I'll run for it as soon as--
whaah!
What the hell happened?
( Groans ) I can't feel my body.
( Groans )
( Deep sea king chuckles )
Lightning Max: Damn it.
Arrogant guppy.
Lightning flying backwards
roundhouse kick!
Hero #4: I'm the class-s hero,
puri-puri prisoner.
I escaped prison
just to see you.
- Sonic: Well, well.
- Puri-puri prisoner: Hmm?
Sonic: Imagine that,
a hero serving time in prison.
I took a cue from you
and decided to escape as well.
Thanks for that.
Puri-puri prisoner:
Prisoner number 4188.
- The name's Sonic, right?
- Sonic: Hmm?
Puri-puri prisoner:
You surprised I know?
I check up on all the boys
who catch my eye.
I'm serving a life sentence
'cause I can't seem
to control myself.
I see a beautiful man,
and I take him.
Deep sea king: Well, well.
More soldiers have come for me?
Goodness.
My fins are quivering.
( Laughs )
Puri-puri prisoner: My!
I feel the strength
erupting out of him.
Hang back, Sonic, dear
( deep sea king laughing )
Class a, rank 11, sweet stinger
and class a, rank 20,
lightning Max,
I fancied
both of those lovelies.
Then you show up out of nowhere
and ruin them!
Now that genos passed me,
I rank lowest in my class,
but I'm still class s,
unlike those two
you've defeated.
I'll start things off
at half power
to Gauge how much you can take.
( Yells )
( Gasps )
Raah!
You made me rip
the hand-knit sweater
my boyfriend made for me!
I will never forgive you,
you bastard!
Deep sea king: Mmm.
A delectable slab of meat,
prime and tasty.
You've whet my appetite.
( Puri-puri prisoner grunts )
( Growls )
Deep sea king: Huh?
Oh, dear.
Deep sea king: I felt that...
( Bones pop )
Just a little.
Puri-puri prisoner:
I felt that as well,
a little. ( Snorts )
Sonic: Puri-puri prisoner
is acting tough,
but I can tell
that he's hurting.
So this is what a fight
between a demon-level monster
and a class-s hero looks like?
It's almost comical.
Neither one of them
could defeat me.
Puri-puri prisoner: Damn it.
His punch was stronger
than I expected.
Even so, I must not lose to him.
I can't have any more of my boys
so savagely destroyed
by this monster.
( Aloud )
I have no choice.
Gotta go all out.
Ready.
Transform!
Deep sea king: Huh?
Puri-puri prisoner:
Puri-puri prisoner, angel style!
Sonic: He's naked,
and he's definitely no angel,
nor is he human.
Nor do I want to watch.
I'm outta here.
Puri-puri prisoner:
No one's seen my angel style
and lived to tell
about it, fish man.
Sonic:
All the more reason to leave.
Deep sea king: Quite unsightly.
Puri-puri prisoner: Are those...
Your last words?!
Yaah!
Deep sea king: Huh?
( Puri-puri prisoner yells )
Angel rush!
( Yelling )
( Genos gasps )
Elevated energy levels nearby.
Found them.
Damn it.
I have no way to reach master.
It cannot be helped.
( Puri-puri prisoner panting )
Deep sea king: Done with
your little combo, human?
( Puri-puri prisoner gasps )
Deep sea king:
Felt that, too,
just a little.
Hear me.
The objective
of a combination move
is to finish your opponent.
Each separate attack must be
delivered with intent to kill,
like this!
Isn't this fun?
Sonic: All right, who are you?
Deep sea king:
I am the deep sea king.
As lord of the clan
of the seafolk,
I claim this world
as mine to rule.
Do you dare defy me
as well, human?
Sonic: Hah! You don't honestly
think you have the strength
to rule the surface
all alone, do you?
How pathetic.
Deep sea king: Oh?
Then I suppose
that I'll have to kill you.
Sonic: That's my line.
It's a shame, really.
I would have let you live
if you'd shown me
the respect I'm due.
I'm not a hero, but you
will still be eliminated.
Deep sea king:
Ah, gentle rainfall.
( Chuckles )
Sonic: Too slow.
Wind blade kick!
Pathetic.
I see right through
your moves, deep sea king!
Deep sea king:
Are you sure of that?
Once it bites, my little
moray here never lets go!
Sonic: I'll make myself clear.
There's no way in hell
I'd ever lose to you.
It's useless.
You may have power...
¶¶
but you're far too slow.
You're never gonna defeat me.
Thank you, deep sea king!
Fighting something
with power such as yours
just confirms
how strong I really am!
My moves are the fastest
and the strongest!
( Deep sea king laughs )
Sonic: Now what?
Losing your mind?
( Gasps )
He's faster!
Stronger, too!
Where's this boost in power
coming from?
He's huge!
Deep sea king: The air
up here on the surface
shriveled me up a bit,
but this rain's helped me
feel like myself again.
Your attacks don't hurt me
even a little!
Reporter: At the time
of this broadcast,
the whereabouts of the seafolk
that attacked city j
are unknown.
Several heroes
who bravely tried to stop them
have been found
unconscious at the scene.
They remain
in critical condition.
Corpses of seafolk believed...
Mumen rider: Of all the times
to hit a red light. Huh?
Saitama: Aw, man.
Where'd he run off to?
Oh.
Mumen rider: Hold on.
Aren't you...
Class c, rank two?
Saitama: That's right.
You a hero?
Have you seen genos?
Mumen rider: Genos?
Reporter: Today as our guest,
we have the top-ranked
class-a superhero,
who's also been number one
in the popularity rankings
for the past 28 weeks.
But the list doesn't stop there.
He's also a successful model,
an actor, and a singer.
Let's welcome
the handsome Mr. Amai mask!
Amai mask:
Thank you for having me.
Reporter: Any time.
First off is this.
We are currently facing
a threat level of demon.
How do you assess the situation?
Amai mask: Hmm.
That's a difficult question.
Reporter: Really? Why is that?
Amai mask: I'm only a hero
during those moments
when I confront evil.
The rest of my daily life
is focused on my career
as an artist.
Reporter: I see.
Amai mask: To be honest,
the only reason I'm here today
is to promote my new song.
Reporter: Well, then,
my apologies.
In that case,
let's discuss your song.
Amai mask: No, it's fine.
Let me just say this.
To placate the public's
fears and worries,
heroes need to be tough.
They need to have
inner strength,
self-discipline.
With this, they can defeat evil
using speed, a touch of grace,
and brilliance.
I find it regrettable
that there were heroes
who were completely beaten
by evil this time around.
So that no hero
ever dies in vain,
I hope each will continue
to train his hardest
to push themselves
to the limit.
Sonic: My attacks
have no effect at all.
Am I lacking in power?
I can't kill him unarmed.
I need to retreat for now
and find a weapon.
Ugh!
Deep sea king:
I caught you, runt!
- ( Popping )
- ( Laughs )
Sonic: Crack-crack, snap-snap.
Deep sea king: Hmm?
Huh?
Sonic: You wait there.
Deep sea king: Hmm?
Sonic: The next time we meet
will be your demise.
Deep sea king: No matter.
The small fry can be let go.
Genos: Who might you be,
and what are you doing here?
There were orders to evacuate.
( Sonic scoffs ) A hero, huh?
If you're after
the deep sea king,
you'd better forget it.
Genos: Deep sea king?
Sonic: You heroes could all
jump him at once and still lose.
You're fine
at playing make-believe,
but when you're
up against true power,
not a single one of you
stands a chance.
Genos: Who was
that pervert, anyway?
( Beeping )
It is the seafolk.
I sense
numerous life signals nearby.
With so many--
the evacuation shelter!
¶¶
( overlapping chatter )
Boy: Daddy, are all those
scary monsters still outside?
Father: Now, don't you
worry about a thing.
As long as we're
in this shelter,
we're safe and sound.
Besides, if it
comes right down to it,
I'm sure all of us together
can beat a monster or two.
( Man grunts )
Deep sea king: I sense them,
yes, so many.
It's coming from...
Over there!
( All screaming )
Deep sea king:
What do we have here?
Greetings, and good-bye.
( Citizens gasping )
Man: Please wait!
We surrender! We surrender!
We will happily comply with
any demands that you might have,
but do not attack us,
I beg you. Please.
( Thinking ) I'm only a class-c,
so I evacuated. Now I'm trapped.
I'm no hero. I'm a failure.
Deep sea king: Surrender?
( Laughs )
I've come to kill you.
Your deaths are inevitable.
And as for my demands,
how about this?
I demand that you scream nicely
as I slaughter you.
Allback-man: I can't win.
I know it's not much,
but all I can do
is buy time for
the class-s heroes to get here.
I mean, look at this monster.
- ( Deep sea king laughing )
- Allback-man: Who am I kidding?
It's pointless. I can't buy time
just by talking to him.
( Gasps )
I pissed my pants.
I'm pathetic.
( Hero yells )
I'll fight with you!
Allback-man: Heroes?
There are others in here, too?
Snek: I may be
the lowest ranking at 38,
but I'm still a class-a hero.
We can do this.
Allback-man: Uh, that's right!
I'm a hero, too!
Allback-man is ready!
Boy: Heroes?
Man: The heroes
are here to save us!
Man #2: Heroes rock!
Father: Go get 'em! Yeah!
Hero #2: Class a?
Man, I'm glad you're here.
- Snek: Happy to help.
- Man #3: Take him down!
Allback-man: Two class cs,
one class b, and one class a.
We can do it. We can win!
( Deep sea king growls )
Saitama: You sure
this is the way?
Mumen rider: Yes.
Since local residents
are fleeing from this direction,
we'll find monsters further up.
Saitama: Oh.
Did you just see
a butt-naked guy run past us?
Mumen rider: What?
Saitama: Must have
evacuated mid-bath.
I'll check it out.
Go on without me!
Mumen rider: Right! Got it!
( Cell phone rings )
Mumen rider here.
Yes, sir. Correct.
We're on our way there now.
What?! Did you say the shelter?
( Groans )
It was the other way.
( Cell phone rings )
( Citizens cheering )
Snek: All right, when I
give the signal, charge him.
One...
Two...
Saitama: That's weird.
I know I saw a naked guy.
Huh?
( Cell phone rings )
¶¶
( snek groans )
( Deep sea king laughs )
Now, why so quiet
all of a sudden?
Genos: You there,
are you one of the seafolk?
Deep sea king: Huh?
Man: Mumen rider went in there?
Supervisor: Yes.
I couldn't stop h--
hello! Mumen rider?!
What's your location?
This is beyond
what you can handle.
The monster even
took out a class-s hero.
We need to assemble
a subjugation squad, and fast!
Saitama: A class-s hero
was defeated?
Supervisor: Who is this?
Where's mumen rider?
What's going on?!
( Mumen rider yells )
Stand-up peddling mode!
It's the roar of justice!
Saitama: Wait.
Is this the hero association?
Supervisor:
Yes, and who are you?
Put on the owner
of that cell phone right now!
Saitama: This is
the hero saitama.
Supervisor: Saitama?
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )