You know the plan, people.
Shu will attack them with
Inori's Void. Once he does, we
seize that second truck ASAP.
The target will reach
the attack point in
six, five, four,
three, two, one!
Go!
Shu, engage them!
Get your ass in gear already!
They're going to see us!
Just pull the Void!
I can't!
Dammit! They're onto us!
Shu! What's wrong? Talk to me!
If you don't move, they're dead!
We need you right now!
Please, Shu.
No, come back!
All units, this is Gai!
Abort the mission! Repeat!
Abort the mission!
Blooming wildflower--
Tell me, Shu, do you love me?
Course I do!
Then promise me, that you'll
make your big sister happy.
Summer's sun clouded over,
the wind streamed by.
The two overlapped.
Hey! Are you awake?
I'm coming up!
Rise and shine, Shu!
Did you sleep okay?
Yeah.
Here!
I grabbed you a breakfast
sandwich on the way,
does that sound all right?
I got to admit,
you surprised me yesterday.
You know, messaging
me for help and all.
I guess you're not going
to tell me what's wrong, huh.
What could be so terrible that
you don't want to go home?
Maybe you can tell me
later, if you want?
Going to answer?
I see.
No. Leave him be for the moment.
Damn that Shu.
Sorry to have made you wait.
Hello again, Mr. Tsutsugami.
It's been a while.
Please, call me Gai.
There's no need to be
so formal with each other.
Interesting reading. Truth be
told, I'd never have guessed
that you were
his son, young man.
Whose son is he?
Knowing that, I put
this question to you.
What's your angle?
Why are you fighting?
What's worth risking
life and limb for?
It's all for a girl, of course.
She's the reason I do this,
to hold her close.
Is that good enough for you?
Liberating Japan to impress some
girl, are you? I'll be damned.
The stolen rock will arrive
in Haneda the day after next.
From the looks of things,
Yan will send it overseas
at the first opportunity.
In every sense, that stone
belongs to the Japanese people.
Wouldn't you agree, young man?
Yes, sir. We'll keep
it here, no matter what.
Who would've thought,
this rock envied the world over?
Would just fall into my hands
as though preordained.
Men have been catapulted
into the White House
by far less than this, my dear.
Such ambition, Emily. I like it.
Still, I wonder what Keido's
playing at. He steals this,
and then instead
of running for it,
he waltzes straight
into custody?
Welcome back! I'm really glad
you're coming to school again!
I mean, you couldn't
just ditch forever.
And school's not
so bad! Is it?
Inori's out today, right?
Yo!
Look who finally came!
So where've you been
hiding out lately, huh loser?
I, uh!
Oh, I'm sorry! Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh no!
Shu! Are you okay?
What happened?
I'll go get you some water.
You wait here.
What the hell is your problem?
Ayase.
I can't do this. I'm out.
Are you hearing yourself?
One terminally ill kid dies,
and you're willing to throw in
the towel, just like that?
I was sure I could hack it.
I mean, I have changed.
I thought I could be all
ruthless, like Gai. But--
I'm not ruthless. I'm not Gai.
I'm just Shu Ouma.
You want to play the
self-pity card? Run away?
How can you quit on us?
There's work to do!
Ayase, enough!
Don't do this, Gai!
I know he'll come around!
We found the rock. And
you're going to help us get
our hands on it. Quit your
whining and stand up. Now!
This isn't my fight!
Shu!
It never was!
I didn't ask for this power!
It was an accident!
A mistake!
I've heard it said, that the
Void Genom can be harvested
if its host dies. I wonder?
You're dead to me, Shu. I never
want to lay eyes on you again!
Inori will be coming home.
You're such a coward!
How'd I ever delude myself
into thinking you
were one of us?
So, you're still here?
Hey, uh, listen can we stay
in touch? I could call.
Here.
This is a brand new song.
I'd really like for you
to listen to it, Shu.
Shu.
Monster!
I'm sorry! I--!
Please, just don't.
It doesn't matter. Goodbye.
She's the reason I tried
so hard to be like him.
But that isn't what I want.
So I guess it's better this way.
It's over. I'm back to normal.
I should be relieved.
Inori, how do I forget you?
Major General Yan is
heading home for a little while,
and he's taking some
top-secret stuff with him!
It's our job to make sure
that bird gets airborne!
Let's do this thing! Booyah!
The Major General should be
taking the stage any moment now.
--Daryl, I know--
--Excuse us.
I'm doing this more and more.
Am I running out of time?
Gai?
Tell me something.
Am I a monster?
Did Shu call you one? It doesn't
matter. Unless you love him?
Do I love him, Gai? This
feeling I have, could that be
what it is? Could it be love?
So, in the end
you choose him, too.
For now, just survive.
We'll talk about it
again later.
Excuse me, sir?
Dammit, Keido, what in
the hell were you thinking?
Using Kurosu's ID
to steal that rock,
and then handing
it over to Yan?
Seriously, do you have anything
to say in your own defense?
I saw a familiar face on the
island. They grow up so fast,
don't they?
Don't you drag him into it!
It's too late for that.
He has the king's power,
that boy of yours.
Oh, no, Shu!
He has the Void Genome?
There's more, my dear.
Seems he's thick as thieves
with Funeral Parlor.
All thanks to that
girl, Inori Yuzuriha.
Tell me, did you really think
a beauty of her caliber
was with your son by some
coincidence of the heart?
It's time.
All right. Take the door!
We'll reach Point B
in 30 seconds.
Gotcha!
Just remember I can't control
all of the security cameras
past there,
so be careful, okay?
All units listen up!
We only have thirty minutes
until that transport
is airborne.
My team will seize
the plane within that window.
After we announce the seizure,
the Endlave unit will
take the field and back us up.
Got it?
Affirmative!
Aye-aye!
You dragged me out here,
so you better get this right.
That's the idea.
Major General Yan, sir!
Have yourself a good flight!
I assume the plane
is ready for us, Colonel?
Yes sir! Everything's
been prepared for you
by the exceedingly
gung-ho Major Segai!
Be a dear and switch
the camera to G7.
Begging your pardon, sir, but
there's no such channel as G7.
Usually, you'd be right.
But wouldn't you know
I just so happened
to set one up.
Let's see.
Bingo.
Are we ready for broadcast?
All systems are go.
It'll play on every
GHQ-controlled transmitter
in the city, Major.
Thank you for that.
This is Major Segai speaking.
All you members of my
much-maligned Anti Bodies,
take Vaccine D now.
I repeat: All members of my
much maligned Anti Bodies,
self-administer Vaccine D.
Hostiles!
I trust this will suffice? I'm
nothing if not thorough, Chief.
Don't come crying to me later.
How're they doing?
They've boarded the plane.
So far, so good.
Something's not right here. But
it's too late to back out now.
It's unmanned!
What the hell's going on?
Gai Tsutsugami! I'm sending
you straight to heaven!
What's all this
commotion, Colonel?
What is this?
I was actually kind of enjoying
the lecture, you know.
Classic lit. For some reason
I find that stuff fascinating.
I didn't know.
Then you haven't
been listening!
Huh?
I want to be close
to you. Please.
It's okay. I mean.
You love me, don't you, Hare?
Shu!
Hare!
Look, I'm sorry!
For what?
What are you apologizing for?
I want to hear you say it!
I, uh--
You don't even know! I'm not
some cardboard cutout, Shu!
I'm a person! You can't prop
me up in the empty spot
where Inori used to be!
No, I didn't mean to--
Just because you can
pull stuff out of people,
it doesn't mean people
are objects, Shu!
Yeah, I saw it. I watched you
pull some scissory thing out
of Yahiro's chest and use
it to take down an Endlave.
I felt so bad for you
when I saw it happen.
I can't imagine what it's like
to carry a burden like that.
But that doesn't mean
you get to be cruel!
The Shu I love would
never be so heartless!
I'm sorry, Hare.
Please forgive me.
That feeling. What is it?
Do you hear that?
Dammit! The control
column isn't responding!
Quick, Tsugumi! Block the
remote control function!
Yeah, give me a sec!
There, she's all yours!
This is genomic resonance!
Don't tell me one of those
jackbooted thugs
activated the stone?
Help me!
I've been sent
to escort you out.
Chief Keido.
Gai!
Argo! Look out!
Aya, run for it!
People are going to die because
of you! Why would you do this?
To grant mankind a future.
Now, let us begin, or rather;
finish what we started
on that fateful Christmas!
I haven't felt
like this since. Oh no!
Somebody make it stop!
This isn't the right song!
If it plays for much longer,
she's going to wake up.
What a naughty man you
are, Shuichiro. Don't you
know better? Of course, I find
this all quite entertaining.
Stop it!