An announcement from the GHQ's
Public Information Division.
In accordance with
Article 9, Section 3 of
the Infection Control Law,
a quarantine is now in effect.
Citizens within Loop 7 are
prohibited from venturing
beyond it for any reason.
Tokyo's a disaster zone.
Hard to believe it's
only been two weeks.
Two weeks since
everything went to hell.
Downtown is in lockdown,
thanks to the worst outbreak
of Apocalypse Virus since
Lost Christmas itself.
No working phones, or internet.
TV and radio stations
have gone silent, too.
People have gathered at evac
sites, living hand to mouth.
Y'know, much as we
complain about school...
most of us students
headed straight here.
They can't get in touch
with their families,
and they can't go home because
of the Loop Seven quarantine,
so they've been
living at school.
The GHQ keeps putting
out announcements,
saying the quarantine
will end any day now.
Yahiro just scoffs and
shakes his head, but I think
they'll let us out soon.
I mean, they have to.
Shu?
So, on the roof again.
Uh-huh.
Guess I am.
Gai.
It's all over now, isn't it?
Ouch.
The hell am I gonna
do with this, huh?
Well aren't you a fiesty one?
Whatcha waiting for?
Stand up.
Go away.
No need to get
all bitchy about it.
Chill out--all we're
doing's tryin' to help.
I didn't ask.
Oh, I get it.
One of those
"handi-capable" types?
Leave me alone!
Or what?
You gonna stand up
and chase us off?
Y'know what pisses me off?
Offering to help a chick
and having her throw
it back in my face.
Looks good topside, though.
Yeah?
Hey, that's enough!
You got a problem?
What are you
trying to do to her?
You two guys should be ashamed.
Just offering a helping hand.
You gotta love thy neighbor
in these times of trouble.
Somebody should
teach you not to butt in.
Missile Kick!
What the hell was that for?!
Watch your aim!
You should be
ashamed of yourselves!
Trying to cop a feel?!
Yeah, well it ain't
gonna happen, pervs!
Not on my watch!
Perv? But I was the
one trying to help --
Mind your own damn
business, cat-ears!
As if! I have only
begun to fight!
Hey.
We won't forget this!
Well, I've already forgotten
about both of you losers,
so keep walking!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
You sure, Ayase?
Positive.
Just a couple
of boys being dumb.
Now go.
Get out of here already.
But you're-
What did I tell you?!
I get in the chair on my own!
I don't want you guys
watching me crawl up into it!
Come on.
Let's go.
Sure.
Aya's in pretty bad shape
these days, y'know.
Makes sense.
Us losing Gai seems to have
hit her the hardest of anybody.
I wonder if Funeral Parlor's
gonna close up shop.
We got separated from the
other members when everything
went to hell. All we can do
right now is hope they're okay.
Ayase and Tsugumi are taking
shelter here at the school,
disguised as students.
And Gai is gone.
The Kuhouin Group has
been consistent about
airlifting supplies in to us,
so we're in pretty good shape
on that front.
I am a little worried about
how much vaccine we're using,
though.
We gotta keep
the virus at bay.
We're gonna need a stockpile.
Think the old man can help?
Yes--of course.
I'll work something out
before the next supply drop.
Is that necessary, you guys?
I'm sure they're going to lift
the quarantine any day now.
Not worth taking a chance on.
It's already been two weeks.
We're gonna start seeing it.
People get mean at
the two-week mark.
There's been a small riot
in Shinjuku already.
Yeah, you're right.
We've been seeing more fights on
campus these last couple days.
Everybody's getting
tired, y'know?
Spending half a month away
from your family isn't easy.
Maybe if people could relax
for a bit, that might help.
Hold on a second, you guys.
Come up with something, Souta?
Oh yeah!
We put on a Culture Festival!
Huh?
We'd usually throw one
this month anyway, right?
Come on, guys!
You know you wanna!
We're in crisis mode here.
Or had you forgotten?
Yeah!
Duh!
Now is the perfect time
to live a little!
Think about it for a minute!
A little fun goes a long way!
I think you may be
on to something.
Tell me you're kidding.
We have enough food
to last us quite a while.
Keep it modest,
and we can pull this off.
The boss-lady
has spoken, Yahiro!
Guess it's not so dumb
after all, huh?
Try to think outside the box.
Is it a good idea
to celebrate right now?
Life has to go back to normal
sooner or later, right?
We should get a head-start.
Guess that settles it.
It's worth a try.
Shu.
You in?
Yeah--why not?
Tell me it's finally playtime.
Soon.
We should have approval
a few days from now.
Meanwhile, I die
from sheer boredom.
They wouldn't begrudge us
a preview, right?
Please, sir -- don't
antagonize them!
Your new position requires
a little bit of restraint
on your part, Chief Segai.
Goodness.
The part after the bloody
coup's not nearly as fun.
Wouldn't you say?
Uh, if you say so, sir.
I didn't expect you
to agree to that.
I know.
I guess maybe I felt like
living it up a little, too.
So this was inside me, huh?
How come I'm even awake
to hold it this time?
I think it's 'cause
of that last fight.
My powers changed,
or mutated, or something.
And when I'm done?
Try just letting go of it.
Just when you think
you've wrapped your head
around this whole "Void" thing.
Tell me.
Why are you so interested
in Voids all of a sudden?
I don't know.
Curious.
No point, it's all over.
I don't think I'll be
using this power anymore.
Stop kidding yourself, Shu.
What do you mean?
Arisa's convinced herself
things are gonna change soon.
She's right about that.
But they aren't gonna
change for the better.
Trust me.
Your right hand is
the best weapon we've got.
The day's gonna come when
you have to pull a Void again.
I'd rather not,
if it's all the same to you!
Aw, quit your
bellyaching already!
It'll be cute!
Oh!
Hey, guys!
You like it?
I don't think I've seen
you wearing that one before.
I'm working the
Animal Maid Café!
You're really digging this
student thing, aren't you?
It beats not having
a roof over my head.
Might as well carpe
diem! Right, Kanon?!
I'm not really the
ear-wearing type, Tsugumi!
Don't laugh at me.
I didn't mean to laugh.
It's a good look.
Where's Inori?
I haven't seen her.
Hey, Shu!
Get your butt down here!
A live Egoist concert?
It's gonna be the
festival's main event!
You totally wish
you'd thought of it, huh!
Man, just think of all the
primo footage we're gonna get!
This is gonna rock!
You sure you're
okay with this?
It sounds like fun.
I don't mind.
Do you?
Not at all.
If you're happy.
Good job, morons.
Throw a festival during
a quarantine, why don't ya.
I guess the virus has already
settled into their brains.
Serves 'em right.
What the hell!
How dare you
just ram into me?!
Watch where you're going!
Oh!
My bad!
But, since you're here already,
how's about you carry 'em!
Son of a-!
I don't wanna carry 'em!
Heck, you might as well
take the bags, too!
Come on.
Why do I have to be
your damn pack mule?
You're pretty weak.
You sick or something?
I'm plenty strong!
You gave me
too many boxes, stupid!
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, here you go,
Mister grumpy-pants.
What is that thing?
Payment.
Yeah, as if!
I'm not gonna eat
that awful thing!
When somebody repays
a favor, you say thank you!
Get it away from me!
Wow, Ayase!
You're good at this!
I've certainly never practiced.
Must be beginner's luck
or something.
Well, whatever it is,
it's great!
Sorry to make you
do this, by the way.
It's fine, but,
why'd you pick me?
Guess I must've looked pretty
pathetic, sitting off by myself.
No, that's not it.
You know, Shu's a much braver
person than he used to be.
And I think that the change
has to have something to do
with all of his new friends
in Funeral Parlor.
So, whatever you did,
thank you.
It really means a lot to me.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
They're here.
Inori Yuzuriha.
Shu Ouma.
Safe an' sound.
This is stupid!
We could crush this place
in fifteen minutes flat!
Not very subtle, are we?
The grown-ups are deliberating,
Daryl, and while they do,
we have to keep our
hands to ourselves.
Or appear to, at least.
No interference.
That's an order.
Are we simpatico?
Yes, sir.
What the hell?
This passes for
a treat with them?
Next time I see her.
I'm sticking this thing right
into that little runt's hair.
Welcome to the official start
of the annual Tenno Festival!
You've all worked hard
on this, so go out there
and have some fun today!
Check it out, Aya!
This is so fun!
Just think!
If we went to school
like normal teenagers,
we'd get to do this every year!
So, where do we start?
Awesome! They have
mini-hotcakes!
I'm gonna go grab some--you
hold down the fort!
Brats're having a festival?
That shit ain't right.
Not when there's folks
all over the quarantine zone
who are barely getting by!
Ain't that the truth!
Didja miss us, fellas?
We were off picking the
gang up some new hardware.
Check it out!
You got a Humvee and
a Gautier model Endlave?
Are those real?!
Where the hell'd you get em?
They were gifts.
Freebies, yo.
You gotta be kiddin'!
Some rich guy just
handed 'em over to us.
Seemed kinda sketchy at first,
but hey, the price was right.
Handed 'em over?
It just goes to show
how we're carrying out
the will of the people!
Now, gentlemen!
Let's go teach those
entitled little pukes
what it feels like
to go without!
Sure you don't want any, Aya?
They're seriously delicious!
Listen.
Hey, you're in luck!
There's just one left,
and I'm giving it to you.
--Here!
--Stop it!
What's with the attitude?
Why?
Why did you cut it?
Huh?
What do you mean?
The day of the attack,
why did you cut my connection?!
I could have kept on fighting!
I could have protected Gai!
Your Endlave was toast.
If you'd stayed connected
any longer, the feedback
would have killed you!
If I could've saved Gai,
then who cares?!
Look at me.
I'm only half-alive anyway.
I've lost my legs.
Twice.
It really hurts me
to hear you say that.
I couldn't deal
with losing you.
Anyway, you need me,
well, I'm around.
-and then the
music's gonna start,
but don't come out yet, okay?
Wait'll I give ya the signal.
I'll wait.
Inori has her songs.
But I've got nothing.
Without my Endlave,
I'm just dead weight.
Ayase!
Oh, hey.
What're you doing
all the way out here?
We're over by the stage,
if you wanna hang.
Not much of a point.
It's not like I can
help out with anything.
Hey, I'm not trying
to put you to work.
You're our friend, Ayase.
I thought you might
wanna join us, that's --
What about Gai?! Huh, Shu?!
He's dead.
'Cause I didn't protect him.
He's dead because
I wasn't good enough.
You're wrong, Ayase.
I'm the one who
couldn't keep Gai safe.
It's my fault.
An Endlave!
I win!
Why are the rioters
doing this?!
They aren't!
That's military tech!
What in the hell?!
Why're they attacking us?!
Where's Shu?!
Turn around!
You'd be a sitting duck
out there, Ayase!
I have to get you
to somewhere safe!
I don't wanna run away!
Not again!
Dammit Shu, you don't get
to cut my connection!
What's wrong with you?!
Ayase.
Here, let me--
How useless are you trying
to make me feel, Shu?!
Useless?
I lost my legs,
but Gai gave me new ones.
Suddenly, I could run
faster than ever before!
But now, Gai is gone!
And they're gone!
And I can't stand
what I've become!
Please, Shu, just let me
stand, on my own two feet!
Everyone, head for
the old college building!
Keep running!
Hare!
Guess I get two Voids
for the price of one.
Sweet, huh?
Uh-huh!
Gai, I'm back
on my feet again.
I'm back in the fight.
I'm back!
What the hell was that?
I dunno!
It's a chick!
That little bitch!
Wanna play?!
Let's play, then!
I think it's time
we wrap this up!
I got him!
Go on!
Right!
Told ya you were useful.
Damn it!
You kids are such
a pain in the ass!
Shuuuu!
Blooming wildflower
I beg you, please tell me
Why do--
It's been a while since
I really gave it my all
with my own two legs.
It felt pretty good.
I feel a bit better, myself.
I think I just got stuck
in my head a little too much.
Y'know, I still can't accept
that we lost Gai for good,
but at least I think
I'm ready to be a part
of the world again. I'm gonna
figure out what I can do.
It's good to have ya back.
Thanks for the help.
Seriously.
You guys, you guys!
We're totally getting
a TV signal again!
Sending the feed to the
big screen in three, two, one!
After a painstaking search, the
conclusion we have reached
is somber indeed.
There are no survivors
within Loop Seven who are
not highly contagious.
Thus, the provisional Japanese
government in accord with
the GHQ has halted rescue
efforts and moved to seal off
the area entirely for
the next ten years.
Loop Seven?
We're in Loop Seven!
Wait, what's that?
Our top priority is the
eradication of the
Apocalypse Virus, so as
to put any fears on
the part of the international
community to rest.
This drastic action will bring
about a new birth for Japan.
So, as the newly-inaugurated
leader of our provisional
government, it's my duty to put
these deeds into practice.
He's in charge
of the country now?!