Blooming wildflower I beg you,
please tell me
Why do people fight
and hurt each other?
Valiantly blooming flower
What can you see
from your field?
Why can't people
forgive each other?
Have you secured the key?
Yeah.
Well done. I'll guide you out.
Rendezvous in thirty seconds.
The rain passed,
and summer took on blue hues
All alone now
You trembled before me
Without saying a word
When your friends
wilt around you
What do you think?
With your leaves unable to
speak, how do you convey love?
Please, Funell.
Get this to Gai.
Summer's sun clouded over,
the wind streamed by...
I've got you covered! Now
hurry and get the key to Gai!
Go, Funell.
...sing the proof that you lived
Oh, crap!
For the sake of those
who have no names
Rise and shine, Shu. You look
dead. Didn't you sleep well?
Eh. Not exactly.
Up all night on the old
interwebs? Or playing an RPG?
Hey. What's that?
Uh. Just some flash cards.
Fine. Don't tell me. Jeez.
There's more of them out
than usual today, huh?
Didn't you see the
news this morning?
There was a terrorist bombing
or something yesterday.
Let's see. Apparently the
attack happened in Ward 24.
Hey, Shu!
Yeah, I know, sorry, I'm still
not done with the video
for the competition. Sorry.
I'm not here
to bust your balls.
Oh, well what else
would you want?
Don't worry, I'll have
it finished by the deadline.
Man, what's wrong
with you?! All I said was--
C'mon, Souta. Leave 'im alone.
He doesn't wanna talk right now.
Poor Souta. That was rude.
It was? 'Cuz I'm trying
really hard to be
more socially
perceptive and stuff.
Really? You're not succeeding.
Well I'm trying, anyway.
You're just too, dense.
Please rise.
Am I really dense? I just
feel like my mind works
out of step from everyone
else's. I never know what to
say to other people. It's like
I just can't figure it out.
So I hide my anxiety and
agree with whatever they say.
And that's how I've made
all of my pseudo-friendships.
Japan operates as a
"quasi-independent" nation
these days. That's how my mom
puts it. It's been ten years
since the Apocalypse Virus
pandemic broke out.
And ravaged our country.
We had no choice but to
rely on an incredible
amount of foreign aid.
And we still haven't
broken that dependence.
Our government is constantly
on the verge of collapsing.
Japan is consistently
reminded of that fact.
Our governance
isn't our concern.
According to them. We don't have
the power to protect ourselves.
I can't help but feel
like I should be doing
something more than I am. But
what? It all seems so pointless.
Blooming wildflower
I beg you, please tell me
Why do people fight
and hurt each other?
Valiantly blooming flower
What--
No, no! I'm sorry! I wasn't
trying to sneak up on you!
What are you doing in here?
Uh. I'm not done with it quite
yet. It's just my home to--
It's pretty.
Really?
Uh. Do you want some
of my rice, maybe?
London Bridge is falling down,
falling down, falling down.
London Bridge is--
So um, you're Inori, aren't
you? You're the lead singer
for Egoist.
London Bridge is falling down,
falling down--
So, what's a famous singer
like you doing here?
How'd you get so banged up?
I need to get this
vial to Gai.
Take this.
Take it. Go on.
I'm Shu. Shu Ouma.
You know. You have to
at least try. You'll never
be able to do anything
if you're too afraid.
Tell me, Shu Ouma.
Are you afraid?
What? What the hell. Was that?
Funell.
Wait, Inori!
Not so fast.
Are you a student?
Uh, yes, sir. I don't
know if you noticed,
but that girl is injured
pretty bad. You don't have to--
This woman is a criminal. And
if you plan on protecting her,
then we can purge you
too as her accomplice.
What are the results
of the background check?
We have ascertained that she's
a member of Funeral Parlor
in Roppongi, Major.
Worthless terrorist scum.
Let's bring her in.
Yes, sir.
Why the hell didn't I
try to help her?
God. What's wrong with me?
What's even worse. I'm actually
relieved now that they're gone.
Just 'cuz I'm not in danger.
That's how pathetic I really
am. Just further proof
that I'm not good enough
for a girl like her.
Take this.
I wanted to take it.
I wanted to be close to her.
And to touch her hand.
Try to forget about it,
Shu. Just clear your head
and your heart's bound
to follow. And after that.
Everything'll
go back to normal.
I need to get this vial to Gai.
Seriously? You're
asking for my help?
How can I say no?
This might be my last chance
to not hate myself.
It had to be here. Of course.
I was told that you felt
the need to dispatch a squadron
to Roppongi.
It was a necessary action.
That can cause unnecessary
violence. I can't allow it
if it's not for an aid mission.
Whatever you think best, sir.
We'd still like to hear the
reasoning behind your decision.
Exactly how dangerous
is this stolen Void Genome?
Well, sir.
That's level 3A
classified intelligence.
So classified you
can't even divulge it
to GHQ's Supreme Commander,
is that what you're saying?
I'm afraid so, sir. But there's
no need to be concerned.
My Anti Bodies task force
has already apprehended
the culprit and they're
searching for the stolen genome
as we speak.
Still don't feel like talking
to us, huh? You must know
that we have the authority to
terminate the infected without
giving any sign of warning. If
you don't tell us where you've
hidden the genome... I'll have
to purify this neighborhood
of every diseased resident
with a sea of fire.
This was your decision.
Attention all units. All area
residents have been designated
as Stage Four infected. Begin
infection control protocol.
What do you want us
to do with the girl?
Wait 'til the purge is over
and dump her body outside.
Is this it?
Hey, school boy.
Uh, yeah?
Hey. That thing work?
Huh? What thing?
This thing. The rice cooker.
Oh, uh. It works, but I'm pretty
sure it doesn't cook rice.
Leave it.
Uh. I can't do that-
Don't mess with me, kid.
Put it down and walk away.
I wish I could, but it
doesn't belong to me!
She risked her life to protect
it. So I can't! I'm sorry!
Well. Look at all these corpses.
Huh? What corpses?
I'm afraid you boys got
yourself into a situation
you're gonna have
to die your way out of.
So you already look like
a bunch of corpses to me.
Dude, is that Gai?
Damn!
You got some balls, pretty boy.
Holy shit! It is him!
Um, I'm not with them.
And you don't need Funell.
Now let go!
You're Shu Ouma?
Last I checked, there should've
been a girl with that.
Well she. I.
You abandon her?
Heads up! The GHQ
whitecoats have launched
a full scale attack!
Evil bastards. Damn them.
They're opening fire
on anyone they see.
Tsugumi. You got
an update on our units?
They just came
online-Incoming enemy!
Beat it! You're in the way!
Run, Shu! And don't
you dare let go of that!
Treat it better
than you did Inori!
Alright. What exactly
does that guy think I can do?
How many targets?
I can't get a count.
They just keep coming!
Get it together, dammit!
Back it up, pal!
Inori!
C'mon, Shu! Do something out
of character for a change!
What the hell?
What is this?
Shu. Please, Shu.
Don't be scared. You can use me.
Take it this time,
Shu. Go ahead.
Who are you?
The power you're feeling.
That is the power of
the Guilty Crown, released
by the bond between two hearts.
What's happening? What is this?