Jun! Are you okay?
What's wrong?
I appreciate your cooperation.
Try not to beat
yourself up over this.
No one will blame you
for wanting to live.
That's disappointing.
I hate it when they get away.
But at least we know that
we're on the right track.
Okay, we're ready
to roll! You're distraught
over the news of your
lover's death. Action!
One week? That seems
like kind of a long time
for the leader to be away.
Some matters require me
to show up in person.
Just enjoy being a normal
student for a few days.
Yeah, right. I'm pretty sure
I can manage that.
It can't be true.
I don't believe it.
Cut, cut!
Shu just doesn't seem
the same to me lately.
It's like he's gotten
bolder or something.
It's almost like
he's a different person.
Maybe something happened
back in Oshima?
Huh?
A vacation on a southern island,
talk about a perfect place
for romance! Maybe he
finally became a man.
Stop torturing me!
But seriously, life rarely goes
the way we want it to, does it?
You still haven't
heard from Yahiro?
I even checked at the orphanage,
but they haven't seen him.
We used to spend hours
playing there together
when we were kids.
The object of my affection is at
the aquarium? What the heck,
I'm not trying to find a fish!
What does yours say?
Um. Let's see. A tiger
striped teakettle herald's
love's arrival.
What? Where are you
supposed to find that?
Is that?
A tiger striped teakettle.
No way.
Excuse me!
Shu!
Oh, hey. I thought you guys had
already gone home for the day.
Does this belong to you?
No, it's a prop for Souta's
film. It's the lover's gift
or something. He wants Inori
to hold it during this scene.
I think I left something
in the clubroom!
I might as well take this
down there for you.
You should go shopping with
Hare now that you're free!
Uh. Okay.
What? Hold on, Kanon!
It's the sign!
Go for it! I'm never going
to doubt my horoscope again!
What was that about?
I, uh, have no idea.
I hear we've got a ghost on
the prowl. Someone broke into
the Oshima lab using Dr. Kurosu
Ouma's ID to gain access.
I'm rather curious, Dr. Keido.
You were close colleagues
with Dr. Ouma. Maybe you
can explain how this
might have happened.
No, sir. I'm afraid I can't.
Hey.
How long's this going to
take? Your shopping I mean?
Do you have a lot
that you need to get?
Oh! Yeah, I guess so.
Hope I can carry all your bags.
Um!
Uh, Hare, are you all right?
Yeah, it's just that I--
Well, I think that I'm in--!
Damn it.
Yahiro.
Shu. Well, well, looks
like you've gotten close.
It's not what you think,
Yahiro. Shu's just--!
Is that it? That's really
all you have to say to me?
What do you
expect me to tell you?
You want to get into it
right here on the train?
Hare, I can't go
shopping with you, okay?
What? Why not?
I need to speak with
Yahiro in private.
Oh, Shu Ouma.
Keeping a close eye on you.
Was clearly the right call.
That night, they told
me they were going to
euthanize my brother.
When the chaos broke out,
we took advantage of
the confusion and ran. I wasn't
just going to sit around
and wait for them to kill
Jun. Go on and laugh.
I sold you out to get
Jun treatment there.
And in the end it was
the worst thing for him.
Jun!
You fell off the couch again!
You didn't hurt yourself,
did you? You're okay?
It's all right, buddy.
This is my. He's a friend.
We've tracked down
the fugitive Cancerous.
Excellent! Now that's
using your guts!
Do you really need my Endlave?
This is just a simple,
routine Cancerous hunt.
Of course we do, kid! We should
encounter each situation
with every resource we have!
Right, cause that's
not wasteful or anything.
You got all that? Scarface?
You got it, Dan! Just
leave everything here to me!
We've got guts galore
for this job!
Oh, don't look at me that way.
Do you think I could
borrow some money?
We need cash to keep
running and to eat.
Is that it? That's why you went
out of your way to show me Jun?
Please, Shu. Listen.
I have to protect him.
I'm the only one
who can do it. Please.
Shu?
Is Gai there?
No, he already left.
I've got someone I need you to
harbor, an Apocalypse patient.
And his symptoms
are pretty advanced.
Whoa, whoa, hold on a second.
You've got to run this
by Shibungi first
before we can--
We're heading for
Point Yellow-One now.
Be there in one hour
to pick us up.
Really? You'll help?
Don't think this means
that I've forgiven you.
But, Jun hasn't done
anything wrong.
Look this over. It won't be long
before we have to use it.
It's wrong.
This song. It's all wrong now.
I know. I'm sorry, Jun. Just try
to bear with it for now, okay?
Looks like they've decided
to make their move.
Are you prepared
for the gene capture?
The system check is complete.
But what's the point
of using this?
Is there something so wrong with
wanting to get a better look
at your true love?
Let's get started.
It's the Anti Bodies! How the
hell did they already find us?
Stay calm!
We knew that this could happen.
Just keep moving!
You hear that?
What if it's a Funeral Parlor
attack or something? Run for it!
Perfect we can use that!
No!
This has to be a trap!
It's a tactic to open up
an escape route and lure
us in. If you don't think
like they do then
you're going to die!
What the hell are you
doing? Get off of me!
You've got to let
me use your Void!
I have the ability to use
people's hearts as weapons.
I can take down
an Endlave with it.
Do you really expect me to
believe that? For all I know,
you're the one who led them
to us. You hypocrite!
Shut your mouth, you traitor!
Shu.
I'm not the one who betrays
people here. I don't abandon
them! I'll make sure Jun
escapes like I promised.
But I need you to
shut up and let me do this!
Jun!
You don't need to worry
about your brother.
I promise he's safe.
Not that.
What do you mean?
What is it then?
You again, huh?
Faceless bastard!
Stay there, Jun!
I'll be right back to help you!
Run all you want! But I've got
a fun new toy for today!
It'll track the signature
of that thing no matter
where you go.
Not bad. I'll give you
something more challenging.
Jun!
No!
Hey, Segai.
What the hell is this?
It's not what I expected,
but I admit it's definitely
intriguing. That weapon of
his and the Apocalypse Virus.
They give off the
same E.M. reading.
What's happening?
It transferred!
How is that possible?
What the hell is going on?
Jun, no! Are you okay?
Answer me!
Oh, god! Yahiro,
what have I done?
Judging by the
machine's appearance.
It absorbed the genomic
resonance of the virus.
So the one now controlling
the machine is...
Reboot the PINs!
Input every last one!
Hey, what's wrong with it?
What happened?
Bastard!
Major Segai! You're in danger!
Please evacuate!
Yes, I suppose we'll have to
withdraw. Abort the operation.
Yes, sir!
No! Yahiro!
You leave him alone now!
This is, Roppongi?
But before Lost Christmas.
That's right.
Do I? Wait, are you Jun?
I'm glad we have
this chance to talk.
Wow, thank you!
For your birthday.
It's the one you wanted, right?
The date is December 24th, 2029.
This was the happiest moment
of my life. In a few
seconds, Lost Christmas
is going to happen.
I want this to be the last
memory I take with me.
Before I give up this life.
Will you help me do that?
Use my brother's Void to cut
my lifeline and set me free.
Yahiro's Void severs
the connection between
life and death. If you use it,
I can finally get some rest.
That can't be right. It's crazy.
The crystals that
imprisoned my body.
They gave me the ability
to see people's Voids.
As a result, I saw my
brother's other side,
the one he tried to
keep hidden from me.
We should order
some pizza for dinner.
Yeah?
Sure, you should have your
favorite food today, right?
And I'll order it
just the way you like it.
You're in the way.
You're ruining my life.
I've seen the horrible
thoughts behind
all the kind eyes,
over and over again.
My friends, my family, the
caretakers at the hospital.
And you, Shu. You're
probably no different.
I can't bear to live any longer.
Not with this hanging over me.
I'll end up hating
my big brother if I do.
I want to die holding
onto my love for him,
as my true self.
Please hurry and do it!
Lost Christmas.
Why is this happening?
I'm so scared!
It's okay I won't
let anything happen.
Okay.
Don't worry, Jun.
I'll take care of you forever!
You have to do it!
Please, I don't think
I can stop myself
from killing him!
Brother, was I a burden
on your life? Did you throw
your future away taking care
of me? Did you hate me for it?
Well, let me show you
how I feel about you!
Thank you.
Goodbye, brother. I love you.
Life really never does go
the way we want it to, does it?
Where are we?
Wait Jun, where's Jun?
He's dead.
What did you say?
You're lying.
Jun's dead.
Where is he?
I did it. I took his life.
Oh, Shu.