Oh man-- the Diet
Building's toast!
It gets closer every day!
What are we gonna do?
It'll be here in a week,
at this rate!
You're supposed
to be on watch.
President Ouma!
What if somebody had
attacked the school just now,
while you three stare at a wall?
Your classmates would die,
and it would be on your heads.
What a dick.
I've seen enough.
Take them both into custody.
Yes, sir.
What?!
What the hell!
Where do you get off?! I'm
so sick of you acting all--!
You're nothing but a tool that
I use toward the greater good!
If you don't do your job,
you're useless!
Going to bed soon?
I'll sleep later.
There's only a week left
before we attempt the Exodus.
And besides, Gai wouldn't
relax at a time like this.
Neither should I.
Ah, that Funeral Parlor guy.
Tell me something.
Did he strong-arm
his people into obedience?
Why do you ask that?
You gotta stop acting
so heavy-handed, Shu.
You're taking things
way too far.
So, they resent me?
That's the price of safety.
At least they're alive.
If I had done this earlier,
Hare still would be.
I know they hate
the ranking system.
I'm sure Arisa was attacked
because she's a Rank S.
But there's no
going back, Yahiro.
You told me that yourself.
Look, I still believe that.
But we can't just expect them
to roll over.
Help. Help me!
Inori?
Is something wrong?
I'm all right.
Somebody. Help me.
Hello? Hello?
Yes. Shu has pushed the student
body to the breaking point.
Right. They're too scared
to fight back right now,
but that could change.
I know that you're
a Rank S and all,
but traitor-talk is against the
rules, so hand over the phone.
Who'd you have
your little chat with?
It's fine if you don't wanna
tell me. All I have to do is
look at your call history,
and I'll have my answer.
Is that all you want?
Maybe Shu shouldn't
get to have all of the fun.
Reach inside, and draw it out.
You sure 'bout this?
There're no take-backs.
Oh yeah. Trust me,
she made it worth my while.
Well, if we're really
gonna do this thing,
no point waiting
around. Here goes.
Hey. D'you read the message
that just went out?!
"Shu Ouma's hiding it,
but if your Void breaks,
you'll die with it?!"
He knew all along
it was dangerous,
and he used our Voids
anyway?! Screw that guy!
That bastard!
He's gonna pay for this!
This is the last straw!
Go to hell, Shu Ouma!
These reports from Keido's
administration are useless--
we've found no less than 98
instances of doctored facts
or outright lying.
I knew this was a mistake.
The man's nothing but
a rank opportunist.
Ladies and gentlemen, we've
been reaching out to Japan
for well on a decade now.
When do we cut our losses?
Wait. So, we write them off?
The U.N. is aware of your
concerns. We'll give you
the chance to cash out
your yen at a fixed rate.
Ahhh. Well, in that case.
Now that we've put any
qualms to bed, please,
elaborate on your plan,
if you would.
Spreading rumors,
Arisa? I thought you
were bigger than that.
What do you mean?
Come on. Don't play dumb
with me. The rumor that
you die if your Void breaks.
And what if it's the truth?
What then, dear Yahiro?
Of course it's not true.
If people thought that,
everything we've built
here would crumble.
You won't be letting me off with
a simple maiming this time,
will you?
"This time?"
Anybody who speaks out
against the great and mighty
Shu is punished. Don't
tell me you didn't know.
Listen to me.
We did not sanction that.
Really. Well then,
would you care to know
who did this to me?
I wonder, if someday, I'll
pay the price for all this.
All what?
In order to save the
students, I hurt them.
I've hurt people,
too. But worse.
Why would you say that?
I'm the one who hurt
Arisa. Or think I am.
You mean you don't know?
She spoke, but, I couldn't
even hear the words.
Just that you were in trouble.
I started to shudder,
and when I woke up, blood.
I'm so afraid of myself. I'm
a monster. You were right-
Don't say that.
You'll be fine.
I'm king, remember?
No one here can touch you.
If anyone tries anything,
they'll have to go
through me first.
Shu, I found out who
was responsible for
the attack on Arisa.
Really. Do tell.
It was Inori. Arisa told me,
and I believe her.
She'll heal. Let it go.
That's not an
option, Shu. Look.
Maybe you haven't noticed,
but we are hanging on here
by a thread.
If you start flouting your own
laws and playing favorites
with your girlf--
Hypocrite!
Oh, you're one to talk!
You knew broken Voids mean
death and you said nothing!
So don't you lecture me
about truth!
Shu, stop it!
Dammit, Shu! Listen!
Using Voids kept us alive!
Shut up!
Not another word! You knew
about this since Hare died,
but you kept it from
me on purpose!
For your own good! After Jun,
I figured something out.
People make mistakes.
And setting things right
takes power. That's the
whole reason I agreed
to work with you
in the first place!
How stupid do you think
I am? You've been wanting
to stab me in the back
since day one! Sugar!
You're wrong, but I can see
why you'd think that.
Guess that's what I get
for not telling you the truth.
Get out of my sight, Yahiro.
The days of you pretending
to be my friend are
over. Drop the act.
Fine. As you command.
Yahiro got exiled
to the Rank F tents.
I suppose he's reaping what
he sowed. Oh yeah, here.
For services rendered.
The Exodus schedule,
and all student Void info.
Not that I care, but what
do you want it for?
A magic trick.
I'm going to take our tyrant,
and make him disappear.
Any of you groups
that are ready to move,
go ahead and take the lead.
Tokyo Tower is about
four kilometers
away from campus.
We'll stop after each
kilometer for a quick break
and a head-count.
Anything else, ask your squad
leader. They'll tell ya.
Something doesn't feel right.
Kuhouin will give the signal.
We'll be ready.
Team B is on board, right?
We only get one shot at this.
Did somebody get
the security team?
What is it?
This isn't what I wanted.
I didn't mean for any of this
to happen.
Nanba.
Sir?
What do they think of me?
The people that I rule.
You're saving them
from certain death.
They won't forget
what you've done.
I see.
Mr. President, the
students are on the move.
So the data we were
given was accurate.
They're headed for
Tokyo Tower, then?
Yes. At their current heading,
we'll engage them
on Sakurada Street.
So be it.
Soon now, we shall witness
the advent of the true king.
I've measured the highest
genomic resonance out of
Tennozu High School.
The index variation
is two-hundred eighty-one.
Very good. You've corralled
them all so well for me.
Let's review the
plan one last time.
The transmitter controlling
those Ghost Endlaves
is here in Tokyo Tower.
Therefore, I'll use
a combination of Voids to
send a high-voltage current
up its struts. If I can short
out whatever device they have
up there, those Endlaves
will be out of commission.
But none of that's going
to happen if I can't
get close enough. Man
your posts and fight off
whatever defense drones they
throw at us. Understood?
Just remember, if we win
this is the last night
we spend behind that wall.
Good luck.
They're here!
Hold the line! Your Voids
will carry you through this!
Give the order, Shu! Send
us onto the battlefield!
To win back
our freedom at last!
Go! Give them hell!
Twenty Auto-Insects on radar!
That's what we planned for!
Go to hell!
The path is clear!
I repeat, the path is clear!
Am I using them as
soldiers? Or fodder?
Shu.
Inori. Don't be scared.
We'll be fine.
I can judge myself later.
Kazumi, nooo!
That's the wrong way!
Let's go!
Enough! No more decoys!
No more hiding!
I'm not losing anyone else!
Time to go. Come on!
Let's put that red line
behind us as fast as we can.
Hurry, everyone!
Well, we made it,
it's all over.
So, then. Shall we?
Uh, is there a problem?
What in the hell
are you doing?!
Stop!
Sorry, girl.
Shu's had it coming.
You can't go out there, Aya!
What's going on?!
Excellent work, Shu. Truly.
But morning has dawned, and
your reign has come to an end.
I guess we'll soldier on
without you, somehow.
So how does it feel?
Arisa! You put
them up to this?!
The answer to that should
be fairly obvious by now.
I didn't do anything wrong.
He deserved it!
Souta?
We're not your damn toolbox!
How dare you use us like that?!
You're a coward!
Parasite!
Just die already, you bastard!
Shuuu!
Hey!
Inori!
Gai?!
I knew you'd come back for us.
Long time no see. Shu.
Please no!
My arm! My king's power
you took it awaaaaay!
Council members.
Submit your votes for U.N.
resolution 17, the
termination of Japan
in the name of global security.
The ayes have it.
The resolution passes.
Instruct the stealth
bomber to launch
the reactive material warheads.
Your king's power?
You were just a pretender
to the throne.
Or had you forgotten?
I am the king.
And I have returned.