Quite a sight,
seeing him in action.
You've belonged to this side
ever since they created you.
And yet you think you could
just hand yourself over
to some human. Monster.
Alas, it doesn't
quite hit the mark.
Please, Mana. Forgive me.
It's empty! But she
should be in there!
Not only is Mana not here,
she never really was.
You're the same as you
were back then, aren't you?
The rarest of breeds, an actual
idealist, just like he was.
That man of yours. Brilliant
though he may have been.
I was never sure
that you were the one
who murdered him until now.
Sorry, sister dear.
But why?! He was
your best friend!
Yes, he was. Tragic, really.
C'mon. Hands in the air.
What's going on? I'm telling
you, I didn't do anything!
Don't move, Arisa.
It's you.
I sold you out and now
you've come to take revenge?
I couldn't care less about
that. All I want from you
is Inori's location.
Don't be a fool!
Attention all units. Dr.
Haruka Ouma has committed
high treason and
is now on the run.
If found, she is to be
arrested on sight.
I repeat: Dr. Haruka Ouma
has committed high treason
and is now on the run. If found,
she is to be arrested on sight.
That's a sensitive -
materials case.
What's so funny?
Ah, the delightful frisson
of a puzzle well-solved!
If I may,
my Lord High President.
Sir, I would give my eyeteeth
to track her down for you.
You're not cleared
to leave. Step out.
I'm going after Dr. Ouma.
I'll clear it with Gai
once I'm on the road.
Wait! Come back! You can't just
flout the chain of command!
When we locate her,
you are going to let me
speak to your mother.
That understood?
Is that your condition
for giving me information
about where Inori's being kept?
She knows Gai. She understands
the way his mind works.
I want to know him like that.
His past, what he wants,
his failings,
what hurts him, everything.
This had better work.
I've got nowhere else to go.
Dr. Ouma, I presume?
You're a sight for sore
eyes. It's been a while.
No way! Kurachi?!
I thought you
might turn up soon.
Sounds like you made
one hell of an exit, there.
Yeah, I guess
you could say that.
Well, you're welcome
to join up with us.
Mr. Kuhouin would
have wanted it that way.
Wait--"wanted?"
Are you saying that?
It was a hero's death at least.
Before I ran from the GHQ.
I tried to murder Mana,
but they already suspected me.
Haruka, what are you
saying? Isn't Mana-?
She's my daughter, yes.
So that girl is
Shu's older sister?
How do you know Shu?
We were friends
in Funeral Parlor.
Really? My little boy. I can't
wrap my head around it.
I've been so busy with work,
I barely know him.
No, that's a lie. I've been
avoiding him. For years.
Haruka's my mom,
but not by blood.
She was actually my father's
second wife. But then-
Right after they got married,
he was gone.
I wasn't her child,
but she raised me anyway.
It wasn't out of
a sense of duty.
I did it because I cared
about that sweet little boy.
I'd lost a husband,
and he'd lost everything.
We propped each other up.
I think maybe we were just
what each other needed
to recover from the shock.
Sooo, there is indeed a Funeral
Parlor hideout in there?
Cross your heart
and hope to die?
I- I swear!
Once more, with feeling!
No, please! I swear on my life!
Please, you gotta believe me!
Picking up bodies.
We got 'em, sir.
You're an honest woman.
Truly, the rarest of fauna.
No good deed
goes unpunished, love.
Someone's coming up.
'Scuse me? I heard
you guys might have
some vaccine to spare?
Huh?
The government's running out,
and... look, we got money...!
We're willing to pay...!
I have two kids at home who
are overdue for their dosage!
Help us!
How dare you keep it for
yourself?! Shame on you!
You sons-of-bitches!
Let us in!
Open up, dammit!
We said we'd pay ya
for it! Come on!
Open that door!
Listen to me! We don't even have
enough vaccine for ourselves!
You're lying!
We're not dumb, man!
Why don't you open that
door and prove it, huh?!
Hey, if that's what
it's gonna take to
calm you guys down, fine.
Y'see? It's just
an office building.
Wish we could help ya, but-
Such honesty. It'll
be the death of you.
Ogumo!
Get her out!
You hear me?!
Don't worry about me.
You bastard!
The harder they fall. Huh.
Uh oh. Where'd
they scamper off to?
Shouldn't we go back for them?
We're of no use to
anybody if we're dead.
Maybe we we'll be able to
rendezvous with another cell.
What's in here, anyway?
That's our nuclear option.
This is! Oh my god!
A Void genome.
The last one in existence.
That tiny vial
is our one and only hope.
If we try to attack Gai, we'll
all be dead before we can blink!
So what, we just
sit here like bitches?!
Come on.
They took out Ogumo--what
chance do the rest of us have?
Don't write off
Ogumo just yet.
Argo's checking
his last coordinates.
How's he doing?
It's just getting worse, bit
by bit. Can't we do anything?
I'm sorry. But once they
hit Stage 3 our vaccine
is just too weak.
Hey, you guys! Argo's back!
What about Gumy?
He isn't with you?
Yeah, he is.
Where is he?
He's with us all.
No. Him, too?
He sacrificed his life for me.
Ogumo.
I'm gonna miss 'im!
Just look at you.
When I met you five years ago
during my mercenary days
in Africa, I knew that you
were more than just another
child soldier sent
out to kill me.
I've shed blood in pursuit of
your coronation ever since.
All that blood-- for what?
So you can sit on your perch.
You can stare down at mankind
and judge us from on high.
Spare me your petty scorn.
My goal was the
same then as now.
You all chose to shackle
your dreams to my feet.
Don't cry when
I stray from your path.
Tell me! What did we
fight for all these years?!
Did Funeral Parlor
mean anything at all?!
What does it matter?
It's hard to imagine now, but
I actually thought of you
as a friend once.
A king has no friends. He
has subordinates. Pawns.
You have enlightened me.
In this final moment, I see you
for what you genuinely are.
I spent years trying to
present you with a crown,
but from this point on, I
strive only to take your head.
Here.
Oh, thank you.
If I used that. You think
I could defeat Gai?
You'd have the same ability
he does, at least. That is-
-Unless your body rejects it.
Then it would just
tear you apart, cell by cell.
I'm such a hypocrite.
I want someone to take
that chance, but I don't want
that someone to be Shu.
You want to protect him.
Being burdened with
that responsibility
was never easy for Shu,
so it makes sense.
It isn't just that.
Using the genome again,
would probably kill him.
We were never meant
to have such power.
This is a party, gentlemen.
Let's pull out all the stops!
It looks like we're too late.
What are you doing?!
Get back here!
Haruka!
C'mon, just leave me.
Not gonna happen.
We all get out.
That's how this goes down.
Yahiro.
Stop playing the
coquette, you teases!
Let your bullets fill
the air! Embrace them
in a tempest of death!
No good! I'm not picking
anybody up out there!
We'll double back.
If we go back now,
they're just gonna flank us!
So what do we do, genius?!
I'm sorry.
Dr. Ouma. I want you to use
the Void genome on me.
There was a time, when your
son gave me the courage
to stand up and fight.
But today, I have to stand
on my own.
I'm ready! Even if I have
to face Gai himself!
Aya, wait! Where'd
this come from?!
No, it's okay. I've given it
a lot of thought. Really.
It's what I want!
This is serendipitous!
Only three ampules
were produced.
I've been trying to
ferret out the last one
for quite some time now.
And of course, Dr. Ouma
simply had it
with her all along.
I'll be taking it now--
I hope no one objects.
Why do you even want it?
Not that my motives
concern you in the least,
but I want to bask
in its sublime glow.
That genome lets you reach
into a person's very heart.
There's nothing I wouldn't do
to realize that kind of truth!
Then let's see if
you can beat me to it!
Oh, you little scoundrel!
Not on your life!
Oh dear.
Drat.
Shu!
Stop!
No, don't! Please! You can't
do this to yourself again!
But I have to, don't you
see? You know it's funny.
This is where it all
began. Only this time.
I'm choosing this for myself.
Shu! Please, just listen to me!
You can't use the genome again!
Your body won't be able
to handle the strain!
It's okay, mom, I know.
I wish I'd called you
that before, 'cause really,
that's what you've been to me.
I don't want this to be
goodbye. I'm so sorry.
But if I can stop him,
my life was well-spent.
Shu, no!
Please, stooooop!
There it is, shining before
me! I see the light of Truth!
Oh, no! Shuuu!
It's him. But of course.
I'm tired of always
running away. Right here,
in this moment, I'm going
to find out what I'm made of!
His missing arm!
Shu.
Unto us a king is born!
Honor him into oblivion!
Ayase, sorry about this.
It's okay.
No holding back! Fire
'til your weapons melt!
Shu.
I don't have any right
to ask you this, and I'm sorry
I have to, but this one
last time will you let me
borrow your powers, Yahiro?
Yeah. Course I will.
That's how we're playing, huh?!
Then kiss your friend goodbye!
You're not a
murderer! Admit it!
You may be right.
But I can learn.
What?
I'll bathe in blood, if it
keeps my friends alive!
I feel it! Another's
essence piercing my soul!
I can feel the
Void liiiiiiiiight!
Shuuuu!
Shu!
No!
Look at his face!
The virus!
Where did that
come from so suddenly?
It's mine.
My cancer. Somehow
he took it from me.
Did Shu's Void do this?!
His Void is unique. It gathers
in whatever is nearby.
Virtue and weakness together.
Light and darkness alike.
Everything.
Shu, is it your destiny
to die for us?
Guess there's no point in
fighting against fate, Kurosu.
If the Apocalypse virus turns
suffering into hatred, I swear,
I'll take every last bit of it.
I'll give my life,
to grant the others a future.
I'll be there soon, Inori.