Keep life going.
For the sake
of new lives to come--
I haven't taken the monorail
to school in a while.
Huh, feels like I spent way
longer with Funeral Parlor
than I actually did. I got to
go back. But I don't want to.
Look who's back, guys! Mister
"I got arrested by the GHQ."
I heard about him.
Hiromi saw it all go down!
Looks totally guilty.
Come on, just ignore them.
Better watch out!
Dude's a criminal, Inori!
No telling what
he might do to you!
Care to show me
the evidence you've compiled?
Oh wait, that's right, you
don't have any proof, do you?
So just drop it!
You're back, Shu!
I hope the GHQ took
it easy on you in there.
I'm sure that the debriefing
process was a real nuisance.
But it's our duty to help
the government, right?
Yeah, totally!
Turns out I found
a cell phone that
some GHQ guy had lost, so.
Well, then. I trust this will
put an end to those rumors
that've been making the rounds.
If anyone does give you grief--
Shu!
They finally let your ass
outta jail, huh buddy?
Spill, dude, how was
your time in the big house?
They interrogated you, didn't
they? What's the food like?
Was it Japanese,
or like burgers and junk?
Uh. Japanese.
Hey Shu? I just have to ask.
The guys in prison,
did they try anything
while you were in there?
Huh?
Do you see any
badass soldiers there?
Tell me you saw some Endlaves!
--Were you scared?
--Were you cuffed?
Come on, everybody! Let's
use our inside voices, yeah?
Safe to say, no one
will bother you anymore.
So it seems.
Hey.
Thank you, for helping me out
like that. It means a lot to me.
Oh, don't mention it.
Just doing my job
as student council
president, that's all.
Arisa Kuhouin can stop
by our class anytime!
Her grandpa's the head of the
Kuhouin Group, so she's rich.
Plus she's clearly a fox
from top to bottom.
Got a kick-ass personality
and she's smart.
So, here's the World History
homework you missed.
And this folder is all
Infection Control stuff.
A little bit of a yawn, but.
Thanks a lot, Hare.
You're pretty darn awesome,
you know that?
It's nothing.
Man. yeah. I forgot
all about that I.C. exam.
Hey, Shu.
You seem kind of, different.
Yeah? Like how?
Oh, but first.
Has anybody heard from Yahiro?
I mean, I heard he hasn't
been to school since
the day I got picked up.
Do you know where he is?
Why do you care?
Yahiro betrayed you.
That's a good question.
Shu, honey! Are you here?
Haruka!
"Haruka?"
You gotta hide!
I'm ho--
Well!
What are you? What'd you do,
strip in the hall?
Well hello to you, too.
What happened to,
"Hi Mom, glad to see you!"
I'm glad, but come on!
Chill out, my little prude.
Hello, there! Haruka Ouma.
And who are you?
Inori Yuzuriha, ma'am. Your
son's been letting me stay here.
Yeah, it's not what you think!
She has this mean older brother
and there's nowhere
else for her to go!
So I've been letting
her lay low here!
He's awful. But he acts like
a freaking saint whenever
other people are around.
So, no one knows.
And he's kind of cool.
What am I babbling about?
Uh, let me start over!
Okay, here's the deal!
Son of a bitch!
God, I'm starving!
Huh?
You hungry, Inori?
'Cause I'm buying.
The choices are pizza,
pizza, and pizza.
Ooh, and cake for dessert.
That's happening. Shu.
Go get it, would you?
What, now?
I need more than beer,
silly! You can tell me
the whole story over dinner!
Gai, are you sure
you're okay with Shu
going back to school again?
Better for him
to hide in plain sight.
Inori's there with him,
if nothing else.
Listen. These last
few missions have left us
dangerously low
in terms of supplies.
We got some money
out of the OAU, didn't we?
The issue's not inadequate
funding. We need a benefactor
to do the purchasing
on our behalf.
Funeral Parlor is
in need of a partner.
There are external
factors at work, sir.
Yes, the Kuhouin Group's
overall market share
is down 25 points
from last year.
But with the GHQ putting Article
301 into effect last month,
we're just lucky
it's not even lower.
I don't pay you
to feed me excuses.
Next time,
you bring me results.
Arisa, my dear. You'll accompany
me to the party tomorrow.
With pleasure, Grandfather.
You'll have to deal
with all this backroom
skullduggery someday.
Best see it in action.
You're right, sir.
I won't let you down. Such is
my duty, as Arisa Kuhouin.
Good job, kiddo,
she's cute! A little weird,
but whatever.
Something about her
you just want to take
care of, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
It's like. Inori is way
stronger than I am, but.
She can be really
fragile sometimes, too.
Cut it out! Stop being
all clingy and drunk.
Oh, you're too grown up
for hugs? Is that it?
Knock yourself out
I don't care.
Jackpot!
Isn't it gorgeous?
If I wear this dress,
I'm sure to knock them
dead tomorrow night!
I know that I'm new around
here. But I'm sure my gumption
will be knocking you
dead soon enough!
It's all about attitude with
me, men! Go big or go home!
Uh, I'm not trying
to be disrespectful,
Colonel Eagleman,
but I don't think.
Dan!
"Colonel" is so stuffy, and
I'm tryin' to keep it real!
Just call me Dan!
Colonel Dan, sir, these Dragoons
are surface-to-air missiles.
So, they weren't
exactly designed
to be fired horizontally.
We can do this!
Flying up takes oomph! But going
sideways should be easier!
You have a target
in mind, or should we
just fire them at will?
Good question, Scarface!
That's what I'm talking about!
It's Segai.
An anti-GHQ Japanese national
is having a fancy party
at sea, fellas! I'd bet my
backside he's sailing out
past quarantined waters to make
some deal with the enemy.
Where exactly
did you get that intel?
Oh, it was an anonymous tip
from a concerned citizen.
Most of you Japanese don't
have a chip on your shoulder.
You realize how totally
screwed you'd be without
the good ol' GHQ
bailing you out!
It's been ten long years
since we ceded control
of our nation to the GHQ.
Judging by their apathy,
our countrymen are happy
to let this occupation continue.
But Japan is our land. The time
has long since come for us
to stand on our own two feet
and hold our heads high!
You seem a bit nervous, Shu.
Of course I'm nervous!
You called me about this
at the absolute last minute!
Should've declined.
Yeah that would
have gone over well.
So, what are we doing here?
There's someone with whom I
wish to speak. But they don't
make themselves available
to the public very often.
And you figured
we'd just party-crash
and force ourselves on him?
In a nutshell, yeah.
I didn't think you'd do me
the honor of coming tonight.
Did you tell Keido about this?
No.
After all, what took place
is in part my responsibility.
What happened was tragic.
But it was just an accident.
Haruka?
I didn't know this was the party
she needed that dress for!
Sorry about that.
Shu Ouma? What on earth
are you doing here?
Gotta go!
Wait a second!
Gai!
I'm tagging out! Bye!
Shu Ouma, stop running
this instant!
Step aside. Or can't
you see I'm in a hurry?
I'm sorry. You reminded me
of a childhood friend.
Is that so?
Indeed. She was my
beloved Catherine.
The best pet armadillo
a boy ever had.
You really do remind me so much
of her, the adorable way she'd
curl up into a tight little ball
to protect herself from danger.
You deserve better than having
to serve as a GHQ errand-boy.
Not at all, sir. The Leucocyte
Plan has been foiled;
after all, it's only natural
that the Anti Bodies
be disbanded for now.
What about Daryl and Rowan?
Should've run when
they had the chance.
Now they're stuck
helping the quarterback
with his little game plan.
The Dragoons are ready
to be fired sideways, sir.
Right on, guys!
That was some good hustle!
And call me Dan, remember?
You have got to be kidding me!
Where's our target?
It's en route from
Point L-11 to Point R-22,
just like your
anonymous tipster said.
I'm Haruka, Sephirah Genomics.
It's a pleasure.
I've never seen her doing
anything work-related before.
Shu! You got to find Gai! GHQ
SAMs are locking onto the ship!
What's a SAM?
Tactical missiles! One hit
and everyone on board is dead!
Haruka!
You have to
get off that thing now!
There should be life rafts!
Grab Gai and run for it!
No way!
If I run, what happens to all
the other people on the ship?
It's not on you to save them!
She's right. And what
could you possibly do?
We'll figure something out.
We don't have a choice!
I don't recall sending
you an invitation,
Gai Tsutsugami
of Funeral Parlor.
I trust that it was
nothing more than
a harmless oversight
on your part.
Do you, now.
I come to you with
a proposition. To save Japan.
Gai!
Excuse me.
Tsugumi just told me
that GHQ missiles
are locking onto the ship!
They want us dead that badly?
Give me your orders,
Gai! I'm not going
to let them kill
all these people!
Meet me up on the quarterdeck.
I'll be there in five.
I'll be there. Understood!
Hold on to your ass,
traitor! You just messed with
the wrong colonel!
Ready! Fire!
I will save them!
Miss Arisa? Might I have
the pleasure of this dance?
Ignore him;
I'm the better dancer.
Hah! That's nonsense.
Hey, who the hell
do you think you are?
Sorry, gents!
Her dance-card just filled up.
Less than a minute till impact!
Let go of me! I've never met
a ruder man in all of my life!
Many thanks. It's good to know
I'm making an impression.
Just who are you?
Close your eyes.
For my next trick. I'll cast
a spell on you. One that will
allow you to become
your true self.
My true self?
Yes, the one you hide away.
I'm going to count down
from three. And then,
you will open your eyes.
Three, two, one. Voila!
Ouma?
I'm sorry!
It's about to hit!
The missile has!
Wait, it's gone!
Come again?!
Impossible! Something must
be wrong with the sensors.
We just weren't gung-ho enough!
What?
Only one thing to do!
This time we'll just
have to fire them all!
All?
Right! Time for some
piss and vinegar!
Fire!
You've got more
Dragoons inbound!
One, two--scratch
that! A ton of them!
Copy!
I'm on it!
There is the shield
of a coward.
That protects
the frightened heart.
That is your Void, Arisa.
Your flaw and triumph.
Hey, guys!
Why aren't you firing, huh?
There's nothing left, to fire.
I admit, your claims of being
able to defend against
a second-order
Leucocyte were valid.
That live demonstration
of yours is hard to argue with.
Very well, you have a deal.
Thank you very much, sir. I'll
inform Gai of your decision.
Good news for once.
The Kuhouin Group has agreed
to facilitate the routing
of our supplies within Japan.
All right!
So I can plug
into Steiner again?
Hey guys, we still don't
know how the GHQ heard
about that party on
the boat to start with.
It was an anonymous tip
from a concerned citizen.
Huh?
Concerned that they wouldn't
take the bait if we didn't
hand it to them,
that is. Well played, Gai.
You got a bit woozy
and fainted up on deck.
Do you remember anything?
No, but thank you for being
enough of a gentleman
to bring me here.
You talk in your sleep,
you know?
Eavesdropping? A true gentleman
would never do that!
Just terrible at this sort
of thing, aren't you?
At what? In all I do, I've been
trained to be the very best!
What am I terrible at?
At letting people near you.
Have fun at school!
Hey! Would you get back
in the apartment already,
you're half naked!
Okay!
Why does she do that?
You enjoy each other,
don't you?
Huh?
Right? You two have fun.
Hey, Inori?
You know for the first time,
I'm kind of glad that
I can pull out Voids.
Good.
I promise. I'll protect Shu.
Just like you'd want me to.