We'll always offer funeral songs
to those who've been selected
out of this life. Hence the name
of our group. We oppose GHQ.
Who carelessly treat our country
as though it belongs to them.
We've declared war on them
and we won't allow them
to select us out,
nor our fellow citizens.
Well I don't know how you
could've missed this news, but.
A national emergency has
been issued. Looks like GHQ's
cracking down after yesterday's
incident in Roppongi.
If you've heard any info
about this Funeral Parlor.
Rumors or whatever,
anything at all, you need
to immediately report
it to the authorities.
Oh, and one last thing
before we get started.
Our class has a new transfer
student joining us. Come on in.
Woah, check it out!
Hey, she's hot!
Everyone. This is Inori.
No way. This can't be real.
What's up with him?
Wait. Do I know her?
Inori?
Whoa. Seriously?
From Egoist? It is not!
Of course it is.
Awesome!
Hi, I'm Kanon Kusama. I'm the
rep for our class. So I'm--
I made it pretty clear that
I didn't want to join
Funeral Parlor so what
is she doing at my school?
Uh, Inori!
I was just, uh,
kind of wondering what
you think about Funeral Parlor?
Why would you even
ask her that, Souta?
Well, you know. Her songs
kind of sound like the stuff
they stand for. So I thought
she might support them.
Yeah, well you
sound like an idiot!
Uh. So, what are
the other members
of Egoist like?
Are they pretty cool?
You think I could
get your autograph?
Yeah, me too!
Come on, guys, lay off.
Don't put her on the spot
like that. Sorry, Inori.
This guy here is named Souta
Tamadate. And he's an enormous
fan of yours so try to
overlook his excitement.
He'll eventually calm down.
I'm Yahiro, by the way.
Yeah. Me and Yahiro and Shu
over there have this club.
It's called the Contemporary
Visual Culture Club
and it's really cool!
So, uh, you think you'd--
Seriously, man, chill out.
Everyone just relax. Really.
We're going to be in the same
class for the rest of the year.
Let's give Inori
some space to settle in.
Sorry if we bugged you, Inori.
Yeah, my bad.
Welcome to our class.
It's obvious. This is just
too much of a coincidence.
I know the reason she's here has
got something to do with me.
One, two, three, four.
It doesn't seem real
that she's here.
Like that's actually
a doll or something.
Huh? Oh, yeah. I guess
that's kind of true.
It's like she's some
kind of CG creation, huh?
What's wrong with you, Shu?
She is not CG, you moron!
She is a real person!
A real person with
real human feelings!
And I'll kick your ass
if you ever hurt them!
He called me a moron. Why
doesn't anyone seem to notice
I have real feelings, too?
And now I've managed
to turn this into another reason
to feel sorry for myself.
From now on, I'm just
going to do everything
I can to avoid her.
Inori? What are?
Where'd these boxes come from?
Hey, wait! Inori!
That was rude. What'd you
do that for? Hey! Hang on!
Hey, stop! I wasn't looking!
Why are you in my apartment? And
how can you open the front door?
Funell unlocked it for me.
Um, can you please explain
what's going on here?
Drop the manners.
Well, I don't want
to be rude, it's just I--
It's just what?
Oh! Um.
You know, I haven't eaten.
Kay.
So, what are you
in the mood for?
Rice balls.
Let's get right to it,
Keido. How do you plan
to rectify the events
perpetrated yesterday?
Rest easy, sir. I'm putting
Major Segai in command
of all Funeral Parlor
related matters from here on.
Segai?
Doesn't ring any bells.
But I imagine that you
have heard of "Norma Gene"?
It's a genetic narcotic
that's been on the rise
among civilians. Mostly
teens. Am I right, Dr. Ouma?
Yes. It was an inadvertent
creation during the development
of the Apocalypse
Virus vaccine.
I assigned Segai
to track its distribution
channels and he
gave me an exact
analysis of the countrywide
operation within days.
So you're saying he's sharp?
As a guillotine,
he's a relentless hunter.
Any prey we give him will
have little chance of escape.
Trust me. He's ruthless.
Sorry 'bout that. It was
an urgent work email.
So, you were just about
to say something.
Oh, wait! We still haven't given
you the proper motivation
to speak up, have we?
Well let's see what we can do.
This is shaping up to be
a real problem. How am I
going to explain this to
my mom when she gets home?
Right. Haruka Ouma. Senior
Researcher at Sephira Genomics.
Only comes home
about once a week.
Unlikely to be back
for several days.
Why am I surprised that you've
run a background check on me?
I'm sorry.
I know this is strange,
but I don't mean to be a burden.
It's um-- you're not a burden.
It's just that I don't really
understand what it is
you're doing here?
I'm here so I can protect you.
Yeah! Coming!
Hey! Hope it's not too late.
No, what's going on?
I happened to be in the
neighborhood and I thought you
might want to watch that movie
I told you about? You down?
Oh. That's really nice.
You seriously came
all the way here
to watch a movie?
Well really to hang out.
You seemed a little weird today.
So I figured I'd check on you.
Did anything happen yesterday?
That's kind of a tough
question. With a tough answer.
I thought so. Huh?
What is she doing here?
I got a communication. I need
you to come with me. Now.
There is an explanation for
this, but it's complicated.
How complicated?
Dude. I can't even tell you.
Anyway. I'll see you later.
I want to hear all the details!
All right! Bye!
Would you say that Yahiro
Samukawa's your friend?
I guess he is. Sure.
He's a really good person.
He takes the time to think
about the people around him.
Not just about himself.
The exact opposite of me.
You've got friends,
right? Don't you?
Is it really necessary? Does
a person need to have friends?
Yeah. I just finished up.
OAU's quite intrigued.
Although, they did
have one condition.
I'll give you
a detailed report later.
I appreciate you coming.
Uh, that's some outfit
you've got on.
Not how most people
picture a terrorist.
Well there's more
to changing the world
than just running around
firing off guns, you know.
Tsugumi, were they tailed?
All clear from what I can tell.
You owe me an explanation.
Why did you send Inori
to keep an eye on me?
Because we have a problem.
Someone saw us yesterday.
They witnessed the entire
battle and your part in it.
I could've handled them
if they were from the fort.
But it seems that
they're an outsider.
More specifically, they're a
student from your high school.
Wait, from my school?
Are you sure?
Have you heard of something
called Norma Gene?
Yeah, I've heard of it,
it's some new drug, right?
Whoa! They were there
for a drug deal?
Our intel reports that they
referred to themselves
as Sugar. But I'm guessing
that's just an alias.
We're not certain, but
there's a high likelihood
they saw you and Inori.
You need to locate them.
You're joking.
Do you even realize
how many students there
are who go to my school?
There's no way
we can find them!
Yes. There is. You just have
to draw out their void.
You see them. Is that it?
You can see the Voids.
That's the only thing
that makes sense.
Oh?
How else would you have known
about the Kaleidoscope Void?
You can see them;
you just can't pull them out.
My. Rather helpful
that you're quick.
You're right I can
identify Voids.
And while we were
engaged with the enemy,
I felt another presence. More
importantly, I saw their Void.
Thanks to GHQ and their
Temporary Disaster Law,
terrorists have no human rights.
You'll be in the crosshairs
of every Anti Body in Japan
if this witness identifies you.
Understand?
I've already described
the Void's shape to Inori.
If you want to maintain
your peaceful existence,
then you'd better get started.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I know I can do this.
Don't worry about it.
You memorized them, right?
The Void rules?
Rule one. "Voids
can only be drawn
from people seventeen
years or younger".
No one knows why or they're
keeping it a secret from me.
Number two. "When you extract
a void, the vessel loses
all their memories of the
period surrounding the event".
I guess that happens due to
the mental shock of the
intron memory
field being released.
Or something like that.
And that one works in my favor.
Time to get some practice in.
Hare will forgive me even
if I screw it up somehow.
At least I hope she will.
Now!
Oh no. This can't
be happening to me.
Holy crap!
He just dove right in!
Oh, how could you, Shu?
You could have at least
told me if that's
all you wanted.
Shu.
You get back here, Shu Ouma!
I'm done for.
There goes every effort
I've made to quietly
blend in. Maybe everyone
will just forget? But
probably not until I'm dead.
I don't get how I screwed it up.
Probably the eye contact.
The what?
You weren't making
eye contact with her.
But that's crucial
when drawing out a void.
Wait is that another rule?
Well that one's not
going to work for me.
I get nervous when I make
eye contact with people.
I get self-conscious and
I forget what I'm saying.
Shu?
Tell me.
What?
Does it look like
I'm looking into your eyes?
I'm actually staring
at the spot between them.
The important thing
is that they think
you're making eye contact.
That's what Gai told me.
This time it's going to work!
Souta!
What're you doing, Shu?
Just forget this ever happened!
Is that it?
Nope.
Yeah, I uh, had
a feeling it wasn't.
But I've got the hang
of it now. All right then.
It's time to get serious.
Let's do this!
Excuse me!
Not it.
Pardon me for a minute!
That's still not it.
Excuse me! Sorry about this!
Really, I'm sorry! What the--?
Holy!
Okay. Can you
at least tell me what
Void I'm trying to find here?
Shears.
Like garden shears?
Kind of. You'll know
when you see them.
What are Voids anyway? Why do
they all have different shapes?
The physical form that a Void
takes on is a reflection
of that person's inner
fears or complexes.
It's like, well the
shape of their heart.
So you mean it's who they are?
Like their essence.
Wait, so,why is your Void?
You know, a sword?
Found you!
I've got you, Shu!
Uh oh.
Shu!
Come on, this way!
Quit running away!
I'm exhausted. Feels like I've
been running for a solid day.
Good thing you
didn't join Funeral Parlor
if you're not
a fan of running.
Good point.
How does this sound? We'll
chill here while the class rep
calms down and then
you can apologize to her.
Sure. But I don't know if
she's going to forgive me.
She's more likely to stab
me with a pair of shears.
Oh yeah? Sounds like you
watched that movie last night.
It's kind of surprising,
you know. How much
you're into all those
gory slasher flicks.
You say that like
it's weird or something.
No, you just don't seem
like you would be.
I guess all I'm saying
is that appearances
can be pretty deceiving
sometimes. Sugar.
So you did see me!
And now you're mocking me.
No. That's not what
I was trying to say.
Look, I'm sure you had
a reason. You wouldn't just--
Shut up!
It's too late to act like the
concerned friend! The minute
you called me "Sugar," I knew
you were going to turn me in,
so why keep pretending? Just
drop the sanctimonious crap!
You and everyone else think
I'm some harmless loser.
Like you just get to decide
what kind of person I am!
And then I have to
act that way because
that's how everyone treats me!
This is the real me, Shu!
Stop it!
Oh no. It was his Void.
You've found him.
No! You can't just shoot him.
And why not? His temptations
prove how weak he is.
He's too much of a threat to
us to let him live. Trust me.
What the hell do
you guys know about him?
What do you mean?
I know this sounds
stupid but still,
I can't just forget
about the person
that I've always known him
to be. I refuse to believe
that it was all a lie! Now put
down that damn gun, Inori!
All right, if that's
how you feel.
Thank you.
Afterward, when Yahiro
finally came to.
We made a pact with each
other. He promised not
to tell anyone about me.
About Funeral Parlor.
And I promised not to tell
anyone about Norma Gene.
Oddly enough, I felt like
it was the first time
we really met each other.
We've got a report from
Inori. "The witness has been
properly dealt with. Further
intervention is unnecessary".
Really?
Is that okay?
They're free to do
as they see fit.
Shu. Do you think
I can stay with you?
It's just that I want to be
part of your life. That's all.
I guess you can do that
if that's what you want.
What's going on?
Hey, what's the deal?
GHQ?
I'm sorry about this.
Sorry about what?
No, what did you tell them?
Yahiro! What did you do?
Hello, Shu Ouma.
You, my friend,
are under arrest.