Gai. Is it?
It's them!
They're doing this!
Dan!
What the hell?
What's happening?
Stop! You have demands?
I'm listening, terrorist!
You've got my attention.
I'm GHQ's Commander,
Major General--
Unit number. Eight Twenty-three.
Don't you recognize my birthday?
Don't you get it? Of course
not. You never got anything.
The two of you make me sick!
You're disgusting!
Attention please. This is the
chief of GHQ's Anti Bodies,
Shuichiro Keido.
I'm saddened to announce that
Major General Yan was killed
in a surprise terrorist attack.
It's okay, Lieutenant.
You've done well.
As the highest-ranking
surviving official,
I will be effectively assuming
command of all military action.
A group of terrorists
have launched
a large-scale viral attack
against the entire Kanto region.
We have declared this attack
a level one state of emergency.
So, as a necessary consequence,
the Anti Bodies have
taken over command. I repeat!
This is a level one
state of emergency!
Don't you worry your pretty
little head, Dr. Ouma.
We have use for you.
Leave her alone!
Haruka, stop!
Aiming your gun at an
innocent woman! Scarface,
I expected more from you!
That's where you're wrong,
Dan. It's pretty damn obvious
you didn't expect anywhere
near enough from me.
It's time to make
our move, Major Segai.
Right behind you, sir.
At approximately 3:40 pm
today, the terrorist group
known as Funeral Parlor
launched a widespread
biological attack
from Haneda Airport,
using the Apocalypse Virus--
That's a lie! They'd
never attack the public!
Now you want to defend us?
Tsugumi?
What the hell are you doing,
Shu? They've practically
wiped us out. I can't get
in touch with Gai or Inori.
For all I know
they could be dead.
Don't say that.
It's your fault, Shu!
We needed you to be there!
And you abandoned us!
A severe contagion
alert has been issued.
All students are required
to immediately evac--
Have any of you guys
seen Hare or Shu?
I'm pretty sure
Shu went home early.
He seemed like
he might've been feeling--
Um, hello? If you can
hear this broadcast,
will the following people, um,
report to the Film Club room.
I know it's a bad time,
but I really need your help.
If they let me, I can use their
Voids to save Gai and Inori.
I don't know if I can pull
it off but I've gotta try.
We've pinpointed their
leader. He's only got one
accomplice with him. The group's
remaining arsenal consists of,
one large-sized trailer,
one Endlave, and
a fighting force of about eight
people west of the terminal.
We've severed
their chain of command.
They're as good as helpless.
Where's the Chief?
His helicopter
just landed in Roppongi.
Everything's going as planned.
Funeral Parlor's forces are
concentrated at Haneda.
Then the time has come to cross
the river of lamentation. Mana.
All right, Shu.
What do you need our help for?
You do know there's a contagion
alert going on, don't you?
Yeah. But see the thing is,
well I, need to get to Haneda.
The airport?
But that's where
the source of the outbreak is!
I know that. But my
friends need my help.
And, I can't do it alone. So I
need you to help me help them!
You don't want our help!
You want to use us
like we're your tools!
I didn't know you were here.
What do you mean, tools?
Good question. Let's see
if Shu will explain it for us.
Well? Go on!
Mana, please don't
do this, again.
Gai, I can stop this.
I know I can.
It's too far advanced to stop.
It's already reached my blood.
The song. It'll help!
Inori!
I've got a lot of questions for
you. But first, tell me this,
is Shu all right?
Isn't he with you?
We didn't bring him with us.
Right now, he should be
in school.
So don't worry.
But, he'll come.
He will. I know it.
I think we all want to know
what he means by 'tools'.
And I'd like to know who these
friends are that need your help
in the middle of a lockdown.
It's not Inori,
right? Is it Inori?
Whoa, guys. Let's not
gang up on him.
He'll answer everybody's
questions. Promise.
How would Gai handle
this situation? Would he
give them the chance to refuse?
If it's important there's
no time to waste. Talk to us!
Yeah, you can tell us, Shu.
We're all your friends,
aren't we?
You got us here. Now speak
up! I think you at least
owe us an explanation.
Would he get a group consensus?
Would he somehow trick them
into doing what he wanted?
Or would he just demand
that they help him
no matter what they think.
Why am I trying to think like
Gai? I'm never going to be him,
so what's the point? I can
only do things the way that
I know how to do them.
Hare.
Yeah?
I need you to help me.
It might seem scary at first.
But I promise you'll be
fine. It's completely safe.
Sure. Go ahead.
Whoa, hey!
What is that?
Bandages, that makes sense.
Hare. What'd you do to her?
She's okay. She'll wake up
as soon as I put this back.
What the hell is this, Shu?
Yeah, it's definitely time
for that explanation.
This is a Void.
It's a manifestation
of a person's heart.
So it's shape and effects,
are different depending
on the person.
No way!
Hey, Shu, what happened?
It's okay. Really I just
used your Void.
You did? So what was it like?
It was kind, just like
the person it reflects.
I know that none
of you remember.
That's how it works. But
I've drawn yours out, too.
Souta, Arisa, all of you.
Wait, you did?
It was like I looked into
your hearts without asking.
I've felt bad
ever since. I'm sorry.
You going to
tell them the rest?
You know, the part about
you using that power
of yours to help out a
terrorist group? That part?
You're wrong.
Am I? Then why don't you tell
them who you're planning
to go save?
Fine! Gai and Inori.
From Funeral Parlor!
Inori's a terrorist?
Then you admit it, huh? So
why would you want to save
people like that? When you
wouldn't even save my brother?
They're terrorists! Answer me!
They aren't what
you think they are.
Those are the good guys!
And they actually believed
in me too! Without them,
I wouldn't even have a purpose!
And now they need my help,
after all they've done for me.
So please! Help me save them!
Right! Let's go! There's no
guarantee we're going to be
safe here, anyway. We might
as well give it a shot.
You make a good point, Souta.
Count me in. I'm sick of saying
it's none of my business.
Damn straight! Now that's
the right attitude.
And you, Yahiro?
I get it; I wouldn't
have had a purpose either.
If Jun hadn't needed me
like he did. You and me,
we're the same.
So this is the
passage to Cocytus,
the so-called Gate of Hell?
Not quite. I personally
prefer to think of it
as the Gate of Heaven.
I can't hold out much longer!
Well, this isn't how I thought
the test run would go,
but I think it might work.
Will Shu really come?
Do I want him to?
I didn't know there
was a path down here.
I've never seen the army use it.
Should get us there safely.
Shu? You're feeling
better now, aren't you?
Yeah, I am. And it's
all thanks to you.
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
Shu!
Keep going. Almost there.
It's open! Inori!
Shu.
I'll never be
loved by you again
Or needed by you again, either
And so here I am, all alone
You always do that,
make me angry
And then make me
cry in the end
Inori.
Genomic resonance
is passing three thousand.
What the hell is this?
Wait, is that?
Inori.
Inori's singing!
We've got our first roadblock!
Halt! Stop your vehicle
or we'll open fire!
Now Arisa!
Okay, I'm ready!
Fire!
Yes, hold me tight--
Barricade three has
been infiltrated, sir!
Do we know if it's an Endlave?
Actually.
We'll sleep with our
foreheads pressed together
The bridge!
This wouldn't stop Gai. Hare!
Oh, wow.
They're behind us!
Souta! It's your turn!
Huh? Really?
They've wiped out the
fourth Endlave platoon!
Gate two has been breached!
You can't even stop one measly
jeep? How worthless can you be?
Transfer me as close
to them as you can.
I'll take care
of this as usual.
There she is! Tsugumi,
the radar building!
Got it! Let's take
a little shortcut!
Hang on tight, everyone!
It's Shu!
A little late, dude.
Inori!
Yes, hold me tight
as you can and don't let go
I want to be in your arms
We'll sleep with our
foreheads pressed together
You ok?
I think it's my turn.
Show them what you can do.
Come on and scurry out
you little rats.
You again? Damn you!
Moron. Showing me up.
Inori.
You came.
Inori!
You truly
disappoint me, Shu Ouma.
You gain what could
be your throne.
And then you don't even
bother to sit in it!
This is where you lose her,
forever. Say goodbye, Shu!
The song.
It won't start again.
Gai?
This is why I can't
trust you, on your own.
Gai, no!
Gai, please! Gai!