Good morning.
Don't make eye
contact with him.
He's the scariest
person ever!
[Music]
Underclassmen
Don't Hold Back
Hello. Anyone here?
Is she wearing
a nun's habit?
What's this kid
doing in here?
Oh look I just caught
the school thug
molesting an innocent
little girl on camera.
-Scandalous.
-Kodaka.
Talk about disgusting.
What? Am not!
I guess we'll just have
to let the people
who see this be
the judge, huh?
What websites do you
think I should put it on?
But why would
you do that to me?
Yozora Mikazuki!
Sister Maria. Hello.
Allow me welcome
you to my clubroom.
What do you
mean your room?
It was my special naptime
room before you lied
and then stole it from me!
I take it you
know each other?
I told you about her.
Maria Takayama is a nun
who works at the school
and happens to be our
club's faculty advisor.
Our what?
But she's just
a little kid.
Don't call me little.
I am a legitimate teacher!
How old are you, anyway?
Ten years old.
You do look your age.
Okay, so.
You said something about her
stealing this room from you?
Yes, that's right!
She attacked me
while I was napping!
She came up to me and
slapped me on my right cheek
for no reason!
And she said,
"So sayeth the Lord.
But whosoever strikes you
on the right cheek,
turn to him the other also."
Then. She smacked me
on my left cheek, too!
It hurt really bad!
Then she said,
"So sayeth the Lord,
but whosoever strikes
you on the right cheek,
offer up to them your room!"
"Ye shall sign their club
founding documents
and also grant unto them your
sealeth of faculty approval!"
Ugh. I checked later,
but it turns out
what she told me
isn't anywhere
in the Bible!
Liar! Falsifier! Poopyhead!
Wow. I can't believe
you fell for that.
It was terrifying.
I was afraid if
I refused to do it,
she would slap me again.
Well, that makes sense.
She probably would have.
Hey! Who the heck
are you, anyway?
My name's Kodaka Hasegawa.
I'm a member of the club.
So you two are
Yozora's minions, huh?
Hello, rude!
Um, I am a minion to no
one, thank you very much.
Yeah what she just said.
Meat over there has absolutely
nothing to do with me;
she's not even
a member.
I am so a member!
Shut up!
It doesn't really matter
because this room is mine!
I'm quitting being
the faculty advisor
to this club right now!
Everybody, get out!
I figured you'd do this.
I mean, you are
just a child.
What did you say?
It simply wasn't fair
of me to expect a child
to behave like
she was an adult.
I feel so stupid now.
I should have asked
a grown up instead
I'm sure they would
never simply quit a job
they had promised to do.
What? Don't say that!
I'm grown up!
Poor thing got
in over her head.
Bummer.
I assumed a little girl
genius like Sister Maria
would have been able to handle
this like a professional.
But I was sorely mistaken.
I'm a full grown adult!
I could be a faculty advisor
to this club in my sleep!
Come on.
You don't have to
prove yourself to us.
What? No that's not
what I'm doing at all!
Oh. Does that mean you still
want to be our advisor?
Of course it does!
Well. Then bow
your head and say,
"Please let me be
your faculty advisor."
Please let me be
your faculty advisor.
Now, you're gonna
have to let me do
whatever I want to
do in this room.
And you need
to swear to God.
I swear!
Also, if you ever tell me again
that you're going to quit.
You won't mind if I strip
you naked, take pictures,
and spread them all
over the internet?
No, I won't!
Really? How nice.
Let's have a round of
applause for our new advisor,
Maria Takayama.
Come on. This is
where you clap.
Oh. Yay.
You guys are
embarrassing me.
Don't worry; I'll take
care of everything, stupids!
We're gonna need you to
clean the room every other day.
But at the moment
I'm thirsty,
so some tea
would be great.
I'll get it!
There's nothing easier
than fooling a fool
am I right guys?
Somebody is watching you?
Yeah. At least I have this weird
feeling I'm being watched.
I wonder if. Maybe
it's a stalker.
Kodaka, are you serious?
I mean think about
it for a second!
Ninety percent of stalkers
stalk because they think
they're in love
with their victim.
Have you had anything
remotely resembling
a romance since coming
to this school?
Shut up! First,
that's not true,
and B, I shouldn't have asked.
Hold on just a second.
I'm not about to let a fellow
club member suffer alone.
Today's club focus.
Helping you.
Let's catch your stalker.
Yep. I'm definitely getting
the feeling we're being watched.
True. This was not just
your imagination, Kodaka.
What's happening now is
not what I was talking about.
I don't know why, but
every single person
we pass is giving me the
freaking evil eye!
How am I supposed
to find a stalker
with this crap going on?
Sena's abandoned
me for a criminal.
Man, why do nice guys
have to finish last?
Oh. They're jealous. Duh.
You're wrong! This
isn't how it looks!
I've seen this in movies.
You know, where the
scary guy says,
"Whadda ya lookin' at?" and
freaks everyone out.
I've never seen it in
real life before, though.
They were the ones who
wanted to come along.
Why do I always have
to be the bad guy?
What's up, stalker?
Uh. What the hell is that?
I'm giving you my wallet
this is your standard
shakedown, isn't it?
No!
My name is
Yukimura Kusnoki.
I'm in Class 1-1.
Wait; isn't that a
famous samurai's name?
That's right.
He's from the Warring
States period.
My parents chose it for
me because they wanted me
to become a son they
could be proud of,
just like Yukimura Sanada's
parents had been.
A son? Really?
Yes. I'm obviously a boy,
so that would make sense.
Uh. You are not
obviously anything.
So what's the deal with
following me around
all the damn time?
To tell you the truth.
I'm a sad victim
of bullying.
Bullying?
You guys have bullies
at this school.
-I didn't know.
-How could you not?
There're no schools
without bullies.
What are they
bullying you about?
Or do you even know?
They do it
because it's fun.
It's fun?
People just enjoy
attacking others
when they know they're not going
to get hurt in the process.
Like killing
living animals.
Or torturing
somebody online.
But it's the person who's
getting bullied's fault.
The bully would stop if
they wouldn't react
and give them
something to enjoy.
And that's straight
from the horse's mouth.
How dare you assume I'm
the same as those cowards!
Anyway. What's the deal?
How come you were
following Kodaka.
Right.
Well, everybody
is afraid of him,
so I thought I
could study him
and learn how
to become strong.
For real? You think this
awkward chicken is strong?
Excuse me?
He lives life by his
very own set of rules
and does whatever he wants to do
whenever he wants to do it!
He's brave yet feared!
He takes what he
wants from whomever,
but is never greedy.
And he gets rid of people
who refuse to do what he says.
All while surrounded
by gorgeous ladies
who do his bidding.
He neither knows nor
shows fear of God,
because he is the lord of
his own heaven and earth!
That dude is from
a different anime!
I always follow
school rules,
and have never
stolen anything.
And women do not serve me!
Add modesty to that list.
Someone help!
Let's break this down.
The bottom line is you are
trying to become someone
who would never
get bullied.
How do people bully
you in the first place?
The boys in my class
leave me out of
whatever they're
doing all the time.
Like, for example,
when we've got gym.
Every time I start
to change my clothes,
they run off as
fast as they can.
It's so mean.
And when we play
like, dodgeball.
They never even
try to hit me.
Um. How's that bad?
Poor, poor Yukimura.
That's the saddest
thing I've ever heard.
I'm pretty sure they
treat me this way
because they're all
convinced I'm a girl.
But I just know
it will stop
if I become manlier
like you, Kodaka!
You are an inspiration.
Not a lot of people
are willing to face
their difficulties
head on like you do.
It's brave.
I think you should
thoroughly study the art
of becoming a man with
our resident thug.
That's so sweet of you.
However.
Kodaka is very busy with our
Neighbor's Club activities.
If you were to join
the group as well,
then you'd get the chance
to observe him in
his natural habitat.
I'm so in.
Why didn't you treat me
like that when I joined?
Okay, what's your angle?
Fess up.
What's the big problem?
You're getting your
own personal underling.
This way, you'll be
the consummate delinquent.
Why would I want that?
Do you really mean it?
I'm gonna be Kodaka's
personal underling?
That makes me very happy.
May I call you my big
brother, sometimes?
Sure kid; do
what you want.
So it turns out
this ten-year-old
is not only a teacher
but our group advisor.
And then a boy who
you'd swear was a girl
ended up joining the club.
Isn't that crazy?
Hmm. It seems like the only
thing you ever talk about now
is that club.
What? You upset about that?
No way! That's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard.
Rasis Vi Felicity Sumeragi
would never allow her
feathers to be ruffled.
Absurd!
Yeah, yeah. Make sure
to clean your plate.
What is all this?
A little snack.
Yozora helped
me out with it.
She said if I wanted to
be a good underling
I should provide
you with food and
comic books, so
that's what I did.
That girl defines
irresponsible.
I hope you enjoy it.
Big Brother.
Tell me you just saw that.
Apparently he's preying
on freshman now, too.
He made that kid buy
all that stuff for him.
Hey! Hold up!
Damn it. Since joining the
stupid Neighbors Club,
my reputation has
gotten even worse!
Hey! Are you okay?
Infirmary This comic is
actually pretty good.
I gotta remember to pay
Yukimura back later.
He's a normal second
year boy, except.
He looks mean.
And his hair is the same
color as dirty dishwater.
Excuse me, are you the
one who carried Rika
to the nurse's
office earlier?
Rika?
That's correct.
Rika Shiguma specifically.
Rika's very glad
she found you.
She's in her first year.
I get it.
Yeah, I was the one
who carried you.
Thank you for
saving Rika's life.
It was very kind of you.
Oh. Uh.
Yeah, don't
worry about it.
Rika cannot not
You are Rika's savior,
and that is a big deal.
Rika feels she must
repay you with a price
that is equal to
Rika's own life.
Wait, your life?
Are you telling me the
chemicals in those beakers
were dangerous?
Oh. No, not especially.
It was only a quick-acting
sleeping drug,
so Rika can say it was safe.
So, pretty much, I didn't
save your life at all.
Perhaps Rika's life wasn't
technically in mortal danger.
However. Had you
not taken Rika
to the nurse's
office so quickly.
Who knows what horrible
and tragic things
could have been
done to Rika
while she was so defenseless!
Horrible things?
Things like rape.
What? You just said rape!
That is generally
the kind of thing
which happens in the books
Rika is fond of reading.
Some strange men could
have come into the lab
while Rika was sleeping
and lustfully ripped off
all of her clothing!
And then, one after another,
in their carnal frenzy,
they might have ravaged
Rika's delicate body!
Pounding her wildly with
their wicked desires!
Come with me!
Sure, okay.
Kodaka!
What the hell? Rika!
Why are you
talking about rape?
Right, Rika probably
shouldn't talk about it
in front of others.
Nevertheless, Rika feels
the need to give you
a token of gratitude for
rescuing her chastity.
-Thanks, but no.
-Nonsense.
Perhaps Rika can fix
your silly looking hair.
That is not a good
dye job at all.
This is my real hair.
-What?
-It's true.
My mom was English
and blonde,
and it's the only thing
I have left of her.
I'm never changing it.
Ow! What'd you do that for?
Because Rika is very
interested in your DNA.
What? Interested how?
Rika has to go back to
the science lab now!
-The science lab?
-Yes.
Rika's a science
lab student.
I didn't know
they had those.
They do!
It's a special program
for kids like Rika
so they don't get picked on
You mean that you--
I see. Things aren't
easy for you, either.
Oh, please don't look at
Rika with such kind eyes.
You're making Rika blush.
Um. By the way?
Rika still does
not know your name.
Right. My name is Kodaka.
Kodaka. It's very
nice to meet you.
Hey! It seems for the first
time in Rika's life,
she has an interest
in mammals!
Excuse me. I've brought
you some coffee.
Uh. Excuse me.
But why are you
wearing a maid uniform?
You're a dude.
It's part of my special training
to make him a real man.
What? Nothing you
said makes sense.
Yozora has been so
sweet and helpful.
Just this morning,
she told me.
Real men exude a
raw masculinity
that simply cannot be
hidden or disguised,
no matter what they
may do, say or wear.
I should be able to tap
into the manliness deep
Why are you torturing
the poor kid like that?
You know, speaking
of torture.
I heard a nasty rumor you like
totally raped a freshman.
I did not!
Please! That girl
was just awkward
because she spends all day
in the science lab alone!
Oh. Is that right?
Hey. I just remembered!
I know about that
girl you helped.
She's a genius inventor
named Rika Shiguma.
I heard that since
she was a kid,
she's been creating
all kinds of things.
Like, electronics, computer
programs and medicines.
She's even provided
technology
to giant corporations.
Daddy convinced her
to enroll here,
but she doesn't actually
go to any classes.
She just invents
stuff all day.
She really doesn't
have to go to class?
That's right.
Just goes to the lab.
In fact, the only
reason the science lab
was created was
for her to use.
They're treating
that girl like a VIP.
Not fair.
How is it acceptable to
treat her so much better?
Uhh.
'cause it's normal for
the superior to be given
preferential treatment
over the mediocre.
I still have
yet to figure out
why they haven't built
me my own room, too.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Well, finally!
Rika has found you!
Oh, hey. Did
you need something?
After a bit of research,
Rika discovered
you belonged to this
Neighbor's Club.
Rika thought she
might join, too.
She what?
Rika already signed
the application.
Listen, Rika, or whatever.
You may not know,
but this club exists
for an extremely
noble purpose.
To be accepted.
You're going to have to
meet certain requirements.
Like wanting
to make friends?
That is the purpose
of the club, is it not?
How did you know?
Because Rika read
your official poster.
"Friends Wanted" was clearly
written across it diagonally.
You mean you could actually
read that on the poster?
And it seems
Rika was correct!
If the requirement
is not having friends,
Rika is confident
she qualifies.
Yep. That's pretty much
all it takes to get in. Here.
All right starting
today you're a member.
Welcome to the club.
Now Rika will be able to see
Kodaka every day after school!
Not that Rika isn't excited
to meet the rest of you.
That is, as long
as you don't get in
Rika's way of
Kodaka, of course.
And you told me
she was awkward.
Hey. Something in your
pocket is hurting me.
Oh! Rika is sorry.
She forgot all about the
dirty book she left there.
A dirty book?
How can you just walk
around with it like that?
Easy. So you wanna see it?
You show it to people?
Of course; why wouldn't I?
It really gets Rika going!
Wait. Isn't that just a
regular robot manga?
How's that supposed
to be dirty?
What?
You mean you haven't heard
of ZZ Unit Number Two before?
Oh yeah! How do
you like the taste?
That's my prized high
mega-bazooka, Unit Number Two.
Ooh. ZZ, it's
so fat and hard!
I can't believe this!
It went all
the way inside!
Oh, it's incredible!
Tell me more!
You can't stand it when I
attack you there, can you?
Get ready! I'm preparing
to pierce your DT field now!
Oh no! It's my first time,
so, oh please
be gentle on me!
I don't think your huge,
dual-equipped mega-beam
cannon is going to
fit; it's just too big!
Ugh. I can't hold
out any longer!
Energy at one hundred
seventy percent!
I'm fully charged!
Here it comes!
Yes! Right here!
I'm gonna shatter!
It feels like you're
about to break me in half!
I can tell the heat from
you is deep inside of me!
Universe!
Cool.
Every time Rika reads it
is like the first time.
Rika's favorite
part is both of the
robots expressions
when they reach their
final climax simultaneously!
There aren't many artists
talented enough
to express that
kind of satisfaction!
You are messed up.
You do not have
to understand it.
Rika does not expect
that from you.
But that doesn't
mean she'll give in!
Hey! Would you like to try
sexual intercourse with Rika?
What the-what
are you doing?
You can't just ask someone
to do that like that!
Please, calm down.
There's no reason
to get upset.
Rika knows for a fact
friends with benefits
are all the rage these days.
No! That's not a real thing!
How cute you
are so innocent.
It's sweet.
Well, anyway, you can't
do that kind of thing.
'Cause, um.
We don't allow
inappropriate friendships
in this club!
All right, but don't
you think men and women
can be normal friends
and still have sex, too?
Absolutely not!
Hey um. What's
the matter, Yozora?
Nothing. I'm fine.
It appears Rika has accidentally
stepped on a land mine.
Still. From now
on Rika thinks
we should try
new things together.
-Don't you agree?
-That depends.
Why am I feeling this
fresh ache in my heart?
Why did she have to go
and read that damn poster?
What's her deal
with him anyway?
It's like she thinks he's
gonna be her new best friend.
-Uhh. Were you talking?
-No.
Hey. Don't look at us!
[Music]
Kodaka, will you please
give Rika your genes?
Will you put them
inside, please!
Put 'em inside what?
Inside Rika's
lab test tube!
You already took
my hair, didn't you?
You said your hair
was all you had left
-of your mother, right?
-Yes.
The blonde is
because she was English,
but my dad is just your
average Japanese guy.
But Rika thought all half
Japanese people were pretty.
Well, they're not!
Kobato inherited
all the cute genes.
Who's that?
Next! This Time the SAGA
is a Serious Battle.
Wait! Tell Rika who
Kobato is right now!