[HAYATO]
Is it true?
Are you going to
marry Zaki's girl?
Are you serious?
[HAYATO]
Yeah.
I just got off the phone
with him, and he went on and on
and on about setting a wedding
date for the two of you.
Although, I guess he did
sound a little sloshed.
I'm assuming you and Sena
are at least dating.
No, absolutely not!
[HAYATO]
Aw, well, that's a bummer.
But you do have
a girlfriend, right?
No girlfriend.
For that matter, I don't
even have a friend-friend.
[HAYATO]
Huh? What'd you say?
[KODAKA] By the way,
Kobato has a boyfriend.
She's staying at
his place again tonight.
[HAYATO]
Kobato what?
Who the hell is he?
Who's the bastard that
made a move on my angel?
I'm coming back home right now
and making that criminal pay!
[KODAKA] Relax; I was
kidding. Bye, Dad.
[HAYATO] Wait, are you
saying she isn't---
Yo guys, what's up?
Hey!
Kobato's here; awesome!
Go away.
You're so funny.
By any chance,
do you wanna go with me
to the amusement park tomorrow?
No!
Are you sure about that?
Check it out; I've got a pass
to Yokoshima Wonderland.
Somebody from work gave
my Daddy some tickets.
Oh, and there's this!
There'll be limited
edition stuff there,
and I'll buy you snacks
and a yummy hamburger, too!
Limited edition?
Hamburgers?
That does sound like fun.
There's no reason to be scared.
I'll be really gentle with you
and I promise we'll have fun.
So whaddya say, little sister?
Good grief, Meat.
How pathetic can you get?
What do you think you're doing?
Give that back, you stupid jerk!
Have you been to that
park before, Yozora?
Yeah, I went on a field
trip there when I was
in the eighth grade.
I'm pretty sure
I spent the entire time
reading a book, though.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
I've actually been there before,
but it was with my family.
And ever since then I've
wanted go to an amusement park
with some of my friends.
Yeah.
I kinda have, too.
Kay!
Tomorrow we are all gonna go to
Yokoshima Wonderland together!
[GROUP]
We are?
School's out and we've got time
to kill anyway, so why not?
[KODAKA]
Good point.
[RIKA] It's a weekday, so it
probably won't be too crowded.
Rika is all about it!
Big Brother.
I shall accompany you as well.
Yay!
I'm going to the amusement park!
I suppose I could entertain
myself with a human pastime,
just this once.
All right.
It's decided, then.
[SENA]
Not so fast.
I only invited Kobato, not
the entire freakin' club!
What, this ticket admits
six adults, doesn't it?
We're helping you make sure
it doesn't go to waste.
Hold on.
It's for adults not kids?
Hooray!
Wait.
Does this mean I can't go now?
Cause I'm a little girl?
You're too young for the ticket.
[MARIA] I guess I
forget sometimes that
I'm just a little girl.
Don't worry, I'm used to it.
You all go and
have a great time.
No, I guess I can shell out
enough to buy a kid's ticket.
You can still go.
Do you really mean it?
You're such a good person!
Thank you so much, Sena!
Thank you, thank you!
Hey, um, Sena?
What is it?
Was it just me, or did you
notice something kinda off
about your dad yesterday, too?
I dunno.
Although, now that you mention
it, he got all happy and started
drinking after giving me
those tickets to the park,
which I guess
was a little random.
You know why?
No clue.
All I could think about was
inviting Kobato to go with me,
so I wasn't really
paying attention.
Naturally.
[KODAKA] It was
probably just a bunch of
drunken rambling anyway.
[SENA]
Tomorrow is going to be awesome.
Isn't it, Kobato?
[KOBATO]
No!
[SENA]
You are so adorbs!
[squealing]
This place is amazing!
We finally made it to
the fabled amusement park.
[KODAKA] I wonder if this is
Sena's first time here, too.
So which ride do you guys
think we should go on first?
You guys?
[YOZORA]
This one.
[ALL]
The Black Dragon!
[KODAKA]
What?
Are you crazy?
You seriously want to go
straight to the Black Dragon?
I swore to myself I'd ride this!
For the record, I didn't stay up
all night deciding whether or
not to ride it like some people.
I just figured I should since
it's famous and everything.
Prepare yourself,
Dragon of the Night!
The Black Dragon.
That title seems fitting
for those who are real men.
Come on, let's go!
Let's go ride it!
Fine, but don't come
crying to me later.
So far this isn't all that bad.
From up here,
all the common folk on
the ground look like ants.
What's the problem, dark dragon?
Is this really
all you have for me?
How sad.
[RIKA] Rika's getting
stimulated by these vibrations.
And they're definitely making
her all hot and bothered,
as they say.
Crap.
I don't think I like
how high we are.
Oh yes.
Bring it on.
Take me, Black Dragon!
Take me to the far reaches of
time and space and, um-- Uh.
I want to get off now, please!
[YOZORA] There is something
so wrong with whoever
thought up this lame ride.
I bet it was a freak pervert...
You lied to me again,
you poopy Yozora!
If I die, it's your fault!
[SENA]
Okay, seriously, stop the ride.
I want to get off.
Yes.
Here it comes.
We're all gonna die!
Hells yeah.
[YOZORA] Stupid shitty Meat
hating hate you so hard!
I hate you!
[MARIA]
Poopy! Poopy!
[KOBATO]
Stop saying poopy!
You're annoying me and
making things worse than
they already are!
Shut up!
Form does not differ from the
void, and the void does not --
Your face is telling me
just how bad you want it,
you planetary mass whore
bitch in heat looking skank.
You're a universal gravitation
streak of shit, which is--!
[YOZORA]
Die!
I swear I'll kill you!
Please, Kodaka, ple--
[KOBATO]
Big brother, help me!
Big bro--
Therefore, in the void
there are no forms--
You better ejaculate faster
than the speed of light because
a pig who can't transcend
space-time might as well
blow it in his pants!
So.
What did you guys think?
That was super duper fun!
Not sure.
Rika's head hurts so bad.
What happened?
Rika can't remember anything.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
may I have your
attention please.
The Official Fullmetal
Necromancer skit will be
performing on the Main Stage
at ten forty-five.
We hope to see you
all there shortly.
Once again, that's ten
forty-five on the Main Stage.
Oh, Kobato.
Do you want me to go with you?
[KOBATO] Let's go now so
we can get good seats!
Hey.
Wait for me!
[SENA] Kobato, I almost forgot
to tell you I just bought
the entire Fullmetal
Necromancer series on Blu-ray.
And I don't think I ever
told you that I'm actually
a huge fan of the show, too!
Which one is your
favorite character?
I like that girl, Mel.
She's from the second season
and not a very big character,
but still.
I think she's got so many
dimensions, you know.
[KOBATO]
It's Meryl.
Meryl.
From Season Two,
Episode Eight:
the phoenix-tamer Emeraude
Mireille von Liveraycia Ohtori's
nickname is "Meryl".
It's not "Mel".
Oh!
Yeah, you're right.
That's who I meant.
And she came back,
also appearing in Episode
Five of Season Three.
Oh, I haven't gotten
quite that far yet.
Sena.
My sister is a
ridiculous fanatic when
it comes to this show.
So if you don't know your stuff,
acting like you do
will just piss her off.
I don't get it.
Man, I wish real life
conversations came with
personalized options
and multiple save points.
Welcome, boys and girls!
Thank you so much
for coming to our show!
Lucky for us, a really cool
friend came here today
just to hang out with you guys!
Who?
She's from
Fullmetal Necromancer.
Now give it up for Guernica!
So.
Are you ready to meet her?
Let's all say
her name together, okay?
Guernica!
[evil neighing]
My name is Astaroth!
Guernica's going to be a
little late thanks to the trap
I set for her!
In the meantime,
I'm taking you hostage!
Oh no!
Someone help me!
[ASTAROTH] I don't suppose any
of you miniscule kids would want
to join us on the stage
and be my hostage, as well.
There's a free gift for
anyone brave enough to
let me take them hostage, so--
That sounds like
a pretty sweet deal to me.
[SENA]
Me!
I'll do it!
I'll be the best hostage ever!
Pick me!
Sena, put your
hand down, please.
Trust me, you don't have to
worry about anything, Kobato.
I'm so getting
that gift for you!
[KODAKA]
Are you serious?
Yeah, like I care about some
gift from this stupid show.
Thank you, but-- We'd like
to ask the mothers in the crowd
to let their kids go first.
Wait, who's a mother?
[ASTAROTH neighs]
Why would I take a mother
hostage when I can have
one of her kids?
What in the heck
are they talking about?
If I had to make a guess,
I'd say they're assuming
you're Kobato's mother.
But why would they think
something so obviously not true?
And-- and besides.
Well, that would mean,
that they probably think
that you're her father, which
would make you my husband.
That's so messed up.
It's totally messed up.
You got that right.
What do you mean by that?
Talk about rude.
Hey little girl.
Ya wanna volunteer?
[BOTH]
You sure, Kobato?
[HENCHMAN]
Thanks.
Watch your step, okay?
♪
That's so awesome.
You got the
director's autograph.
Good thing Sena spoke up
because otherwise I doubt
they would have
asked you to volunteer.
[KOBATO]
Yeah, thanks.
I-- Uh.
Thank you, Sena.
Oh, Kobato!
I'll never get over how cute
she is when she acts shy
and runs away from me!
I want to thank you, too, Sena.
That was cool of you.
Well, it isn't like
I did it for you or anything.
This whole day was
for Kobato, so--
And what was up with
those awful actors?
Us married?
I mean, whatever.
We're not even a couple.
Need to be that first.
And we aren't, yet.
What're you saying?
Nothing, so just shut up!
So.
What have you guys
been doing so far?
I just sat on a bench
and read my book.
Rika went on the merry
go round ten times in a row.
I ate a hot dog, and popcorn,
and a crepe, and let's see.
What else did I have?
Oh!
You bought all that for her?
Why?
You didn't have to.
Nonsense, it was no trouble.
I enjoyed looking
after your sister.
It was an honor.
Here you go, honey.
Yay!
I love curry!
It looks like poo--
Your life depends on you
not finishing that sentence.
Curry tastes really yummy.
Good.
Ow, that hurt.
What do you guys wanna do
after we finish eating?
I want to go back and ride
the Black Dragon again!
I think we've all had enough
of the Black Dragon today.
Right?
Wrong.
I mean, I'm totally down to hit
up that roller coaster again;
it was a blast.
But if you guys are
just too scared to go,
I completely understand.
Don't go playing
all tough, Meat.
You thought for sure
you were gonna die.
Oh?
Says the girl who was screaming
for help the entire time?
Shut up.
I was so not.
[SENA]
Help!
Yeah, that's right;
your pathetic screams are
perfectly preserved
in my memory.
At least I wasn't
the one who was crying.
And, I happen to know you
peed in your pants a little!
How did you know that?
Are you kidding?
You really did?
Of course not.
Don't be stupid; that lame
coaster didn't scare me at all
unlike you and your
panicked cries for help!
Fine, then why don't you prove
it to us by going another round.
Cool, let's do it.
But I'm not going
unless you go with me!
My camera will prove
you can't ride that thing
without screaming
your nasty head off!
Hold on, since when
do you have a camera?
Hidden and ready since always.
[YOZORA]
Who are you hiding it from?
[SENA]
No one.
It doesn't matter.
[MARIA]
Let's go on this one next!
[KOBATO] Don't listen
to her, Big Brother!
We're so high right now.
[KOBATO]
Those humans look like ants.
That thing's no joke.
I've never been on a coaster
that intense before.
Speaking of, I wonder how
Yozora and Sena are doing.
It's been a really long time
since we split up.
Do you think we should go
find out where they are?
[YUKIMURA]
Big brother.
The girls are over there.
[YOZORA]
My head hurts.
[SENA]
I feel sick.
Whoa.
What happened to you two?
Eight times.
Black Dragon.
[KODAKA] You rode the
Black Dragon eight times?
Yozora wouldn't admit that
she lost to me, big time.
Meat wouldn't hurry up
and just die, big time.
Interesting.
Which one of you was
the final winner?
Unfortunately,
this battle's not over.
It's time to get
the ninth round started.
Are you about ready?
Come on, guys.
You don't have
to do this anymore.
Nothing wrong
with calling it a tie.
Not happening.
Over my dead body.
She'll never beat me.
I won't allow--
[KODAKA screaming, gagging]
It's settled?
Meet in the
waiting room at four?
Maria.
Why are you coming
to the mens side?
Because I don't want
to go with the girls because
they smell like vomit
and that's gross.
Fair enough.
I guess I can't
fault you for that.
[MARIA]
Yay!
I'm gonna take a bath
with Big Brother!
[YUKIMURA]
Big Brother?
I shall wash your back for you.
[KODAKA]
No thank you, I'm fine.
I can do it myself!
[YUKIMURA]
Of course, as you wish;
I can see that I am
completely useless to you.
In that case, I must--
[KODAKA]
Okay, fine, you can wash it.
Please wash my back, Yukimura.
[YUKIMURA]
As you wish.
I will not let you down.
[YUKIMURA breathing heavily]
[KODAKA] Come on,
get it together, Kodaka.
Don't forget this guy is a dude!
So this must be what
a weenie looks like.
Bad girl.
Gimmie that towel.
Yeah, okay.
But I don't understand why
you have that weird thing.
What do you mean by weird?
It's perfectly normal;
all guys have these.
[MARIA]
Oh.
Okay, well, how come Yukimura
doesn't have one, then?
[MARIA] Yukimura is a boy
without a weenie!
That makes him weird!
[YUKIMURA] It's only because
I haven't matured enough yet.
[MARIA] Does that mean you'll
grow one when you get older?
[YUKIMURA]
Yes.
I shall work hard to be a
full-fledged man like my mentor,
Big Brother.
[MARIA]
I hope you get to get one soon.
You're not making sense--
[KODAKA]
What the-- He doesn't have one.
[YUKIMURA]
Forgive me.
I'm just easily embarrassed.
[KODAKA]
I feel so much better.
Of course a guy this cute
isn't actually a guy.
Where do you wanna go now?
Over there!
[RIKA] Well, Rika did not
see that one coming.
Excuse Rika for a minute.
Hold on.
Rika!
It is true.
There's no doubt
about it, Kodaka.
Yukimura's been
a girl this whole time!
That's exactly
what I just told you.
Oh.
Rika's used to checking things
out personally, for science.
Good, I'm glad you're convinced.
Can you make
Yukimura believe it, too?
I didn't have
much luck with that.
Weird stuff is all
you ever want Rika for.
Fine.
Yukimura, dude,
come with me, please.
You don't have a yaoi hole.
[YUKIMURA]
Really?
[RIKA]
Nope. Sorry, girl.
[YUKIMURA]
People have said that before,
but I thought I would get
one and be a boy eventually.
Kodaka.
I have bad news.
I'm afraid I am not
a true, powerful man.
That's probably because you're
not even a man to begin with.
No! Wait! Don't cry!
Please, stop that!
[YUKIMURA]
I deeply apologize.
Hey.
Can you at least tell me
what made you think you were
really a boy all this time?
Just family circumstances.
Uh-huh.
Wait.
That's the end of
the explanation?
It is.
I'm shocked that no one
figured this out before.
Actually, a few people have
noticed and pointed it out
to her previously, but she
decided not to listen to them.
[KODAKA]
Right.
Of course.
[KODAKA] I'm glad Rika
managed to bring her around.
[YUKIMURA]
Kodaka.
Do I still get to be
your little brother?
I'm not a boy, but I can't
just stop looking up to you.
You're still my little bro.
It's gonna take a lot more than
you being a girl to change that.
Good.
That's such a relief.
Thank you so much.
I'll always remain
your devoted servant.
Jeez, Kodaka,
why are you blushing?
How crazy is this?
Yukimura's suddenly looking
totally adorable to me.
I mean, talk about moe!
Moe?
Yeah.
The pretty little maid type.
Damn it.
How could I be
so completely blind?
All this time I thought
he was just strange.
Hey, guys.
What's the matter with Yozora?
She's so pretty and sweet
and super submissive.
Perfectly willing
to be his personal slave.
Gimmie a break!
I can't take it.
I have the worst luck.
Why does everything
always have to suck so hard?
[KODAKA]
They all look so cute.
When they're sleeping
they almost remind me
of normal girls.
Big Brother.
I'm still so shocked.
I never imagined
I was actually a girl.
It's not that uncommon
for a pretty-boy character
to turn out to be a girl, but
this is the first time Rika's
seen it in third person.
Yeah, well.
Change isn't always
that awesome, okay?
My apologies, sir.
Next time.
"That Kind of Play
is Not Allowed"
and "My Worldview is
Disturbed When You Are Around!"
Hey, Rika wonders what
"you" they're talking about.
It's you, Rika.
That was a spoiler alert!