I'm Hirotaka Nakegawa,
and I transferred from Tokyo.
Nice to meet ya.
Ha.
More Tokyo scum.
Oh.
Hirotaka.
Kuya.
Kuya, is that you?
[KODAKA]
It was a fateful reunion!
Rika thinks it looks perfect.
I agree.
Okay, we got it, guys.
Let's start getting ready
for the next scene.
[YOZORA]
Everybody good to go?
I'm all set here.
Jeez, this is heavy.
[YOZORA]
Okay.
Lights, camera, action!
You've got some nerve,
you know that?
What?
Why, how dare you?
[MARIA]
How dare I?
How dare you?
Awesome!
Cut!
Now what's after this scene?
[RIKA]
Hey.
Yozora?
The sun is setting,
so we're losing our light.
Anything we shoot now won't
match the other footage.
Well that's that, then.
[YOZORA]
Hey, guys!
We'll pick it up tomorrow!
Meet in the
clubroom after school!
We're running a little
behind so do not be late!
[EVERYONE]
Okay.
[YOZORA]
I can't hear you!
[EVERYONE]
Okay!
[KODAKA] No scenes with
Kotaro today, either.
Man, I wish I had
a little more screen time.
But, being a part of the crew is
more fun than I thought it'd be,
so I guess it's all right.
[KODAKA] Those must be the
score rankings from finals.
Sena scored eight ninety-five
out of nine hundred?
I didn't know someone could
even get a score that high.
Yozora got the highest score
in our class, too.
What's that about?
Gross.
Hey, you got some
kind of problem, pal?
What?
I don't think so.
No problem here.
Hold on!
You're Sena Kashiwazaki's
boyfriend, aren't you?
I-- huh?
I know it's true.
Curse that tricky Sena.
If a mortal enemy is a thing,
she's totally mine!
I'm getting that.
So, no offense,
but who are you anyway?
Are you serious?
You really don't know who I am?
Good grief.
I suppose I should've expected
an associate of Sena's to be
as rude as she is.
Wow.
Okay, are you like
famous or something?
Should be; my name is Aoi Yusa.
Student Council Treasurer.
Year Two, Class Three,
ranked second.
Oh.
Class Three, huh?
That's Sena's Class.
You're in the student
council and ranked second
in our whole grade?
That's impressive.
Your condescending attitude is
more than a little obnoxious!
I don't need you to remind me
I've been Sena Kashiwazaki's
runner up since last year.
I don't know anything
about last year.
But this year it looks like
you're doing really great.
Sena is just tough, that's all.
So what?
I wanna win!
By getting better
exam scores if nothing else!
She's the most glamorous,
gets the highest grades ever,
and is one of the
best athletes at school!
Not to mention she's
a rich little princess!
I feel like I've heard
all this somewhere before.
[AOI]
That's not the worst part.
I know for a fact she's one of
those people with so-called
"real lives." Now, on top of
that she's got a boyfriend?
No one person is
supposed to get that much.
Her existence is a mockery.
It's not fair, Sena's boyfriend.
It's not!
Slow down a second; I am not
now nor have I ever dated Sena.
Oh, please,
don't try to lie to me.
You forget, I've seen
the two of you together.
And there's obviously
something going on there.
The other guys in school
can barely even talk to her,
yet you have no problem
chattin' her up left and right.
[KODAKA] This chick is not
what I'd call a listener.
I mean, geez.
I'm fighting like hell to get
a higher score than her.
Meanwhile, she goes out and gets
herself a super cool boyfriend.
Like I said, it isn't fair!
A moment please.
You just referred to
her boyfriend as 'cool'.
Are you talking about me?
Uh.
Do you see anyone
else standing there?
I mean, it doesn't matter
how you look at it,
you're super cool.
There's that natural
looking blond hair
you obviously dye regularly.
And you wear your pants rolled
up, like the hipster you are.
Some might call it fashion.
The point is, you're clearly
another one of those special
"having life" people
because you're so damn cool.
Thank you.
Nobody's ever talked
to me like that before.
Why're you making
that stupid face?
Come on!
Great, so on top of being cool,
you also have a sense of humor!
I can't help but be impressed,
but I hate it so much.
Fine, you win; I'm
jealous of both of you!
Mister Perfect and Little Miss
Perfect are perfect, perfect,
perfect for each other!
Vomit!
I'm so out of here.
[KODAKA]
So that's Aoi Yusa.
Apparently this place is
freakin' packed with weirdos.
Yo.
What's up?
[KODAKA]
Hey.
Why are you the only one here?
Yozora and Rika left to go scout
out a new location for filming.
Something about a shot of
the sun setting into the sea.
Ah.
Hey, on the way here.
I ran into a girl
named Aoi Yusa checking out
the finals rankings.
[SENA]
Who is that person?
[KODAKA] You mean you
don't already know her?
She's in your class!
[SENA]
What?
She's kinda short
and has this shortish
reddish hair thing going on?
Oh yeah.
Short and shortish
reddish kinda rings a bell.
You should know the people
you're in class with, at least.
Well, I memorized the names
of all the girls
who sit close to me.
Not that it ever paid off any.
What, did something happen?
[SENA]
I told you.
There are only two types
of girls in this world.
Awesome girls.
The kind I can be friends with.
And all those other bitches.
Besides.
Why should I be forced to learn
a bunch of mongrels' names?
[KODAKA] She calls the people
in her class mongrels?
Well, evidently this Aoi
girl isn't very happy that she's
always listed right below you
on every single test ranking.
Why would I care about
another students' rank?
Did you see the scores; where
are those things even posted?
[KODAKA] On the bulletin
board in the courtyard!
Oh.
Guess that makes sense.
[KODAKA]
You mean you never looked?
[SENA] I don't have to; I can
tell my rank from the paper that
has our percentiles
and stuff on it.
The only thing that matters
to me is that I come in first.
[KODAKA]
You really are something.
Yeah, thank you.
What kind of studying do you
normally do for your classes?
Please tell me you have a tutor.
No way.
I don't study outside
of school and homework.
You're kidding me?
You study for tests,
though, right?
Not besides that one time
we studied together.
But hey, that was a pretty
good time, though, wasn't it?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I guess it was.
[SENA]
So, what's the deal?
Did something weird happen
with that Aoi girl?
Meh.
Never mind.
Okay.
[KODAKA]
It's weird.
She honestly couldn't care less
about anything that
doesn't affect her directly.
Yet when she does
care about something,
she gets so into it
she makes it awkward.
When it comes to Yozora,
even if she doesn't like it,
she gets practically criminal.
The photos might be criminal.
She lives for
what makes her happy
and does exactly what she wants.
It doesn't help that she's
got a crazy amount of talent
and a rich enough family
to get away with it all, too.
She's a born princess.
Maybe it's only natural for
all the girls in the world
to hate her.
Now that I think about it,
getting to hang out with her
probably is some sort
of bizarre, divine honor.
We found the
perfect location, you guys!
But we have to
go there right now.
Game over, Meat.
[SENA]
Hey!
[YOZORA] Why are
you still sitting?
Let's go.
[KODAKA]
Yeah.
Okay.
[RIKA]
And action!
Get ready, Hirotaka,
'cause I'm coming strong!
Kuya.
What is wrong with you?
[RIKA]
Cut!
Okay!
We're looking pretty good!
[KODAKA]
Hey, Rika.
Are you sure this will work out?
Yeah, why would it not?
[KODAKA] I dunno, maybe because
we're obviously in a park?
There's no need
to worry about that.
Rika's going to use CG later
to make it appear like the
whole scene's at the beach.
It'll be so fun!
[RIKA] Rika needs to go edit
this, so she'll see you later!
Kay, bye then!
I wonder if she'll
actually be able to make
that beach scene thing work.
I mean, she's a scientist
not a CG expert.
[PEGASUS]
Well, if it isn't Kodaka.
[KODAKA]
Oh, hi, President.
[PEGASUS]
Hi.
Fancy seeing you here.
Well, we're at school, so--
Right.
[PEGASUS] Our festival
atmosphere is rather pleasant,
don't you agree?
[KODAKA]
Yeah.
I guess it is.
Now, if I recall correctly, your
club is doing a movie right?
[KODAKA]
Yes, sir.
I certainly enjoy a good flick.
And believe it or not,
your father used to drag me out
to the movies all the time.
What's funny?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Tell me about this movie
your making; what's it like?
Sena didn't say.
Sena hasn't told you
what it's about?
Well, I don't have as much time
to speak with her as I'd like.
Cool, I get that.
When you're done, I'd love to
watch the movie, if that's okay.
Sorry.
I'd feel a little awkward
having someone I know watch it.
By the way, Kodaka.
Yeah?
I'm curious how your
relationship with Sena
has been coming along.
I'm not sure what you mean.
I'm a jerk; of course you're
too embarrassed to talk
to me about it.
No, I'm not embarrassed, sir.
It's just that what do you
mean by our relationship?
We're just guys; you don't
have to play dumb with me.
I'm not playing!
Um, I don't-- I am
really confused, sir.
It is my understanding that
you and Sena are dating.
Not accurate, sir.
[PEGASUS yelling]
What?
I have to go now.
Sorry, urgent.
I'll see you another day.
Sure.
I'll see ya.
Damn you, fate!
What's going on?
[KODAKA]
Why is everyone so weird?
I don't get it.
Hey guys, what's up?
[SENA]
Kodaka, come with me real quick.
[KODAKA]
Why?
[YOZORA] What the hell are
you doing, Fog Lights?
[SENA]
We have to do something.
We'll be right back.
[KODAKA]
Jeez, Sena, what's your deal?
[SENA]
It's hot.
Yeah.
So, what are we here for?
[SENA] I think--well, it looks
like Daddy thought you and I
were dating.
[KODAKA]
Oh, yeah.
I heard.
Yesterday, he asked me
if we were in a relationship,
and seemed upset
when I told him no.
Do you have any idea
where he got that from?
Well, uh.
Let me think.
I'm not sure how to put this.
Will you please stop
glaring at me first, though?
I'm not glaring at you;
I'm just suspicious.
[SENA]
Okay, um.
Remember how we all went
to the amusement park?
[KODAKA]
Yeah.
I remember.
[SENA] And, well, I got those
tickets from Daddy, right?
[KODAKA]
So you said.
[SENA] See, when he
gave them to me, I said.
"Thank you!
Kobato's for sure gonna
be my little sister, now!"
What?
I think that gave Daddy
the wrong idea about
you and me and stuff.
You're not making sense.
Geez, why do you
have to be so stupid?
Think about it,
if we got married,
agh-- then that would mean--
I um-- If we're married.
Kobato would
literally be my sister.
If we're what?
I guess that's true,
but I'm still lost.
And at the time,
I was just so excited,
I didn't really think
all that much about it.
Now, in hindsight, I remember
he was acting all weird.
[SENA] Like he'd ask, "Are
there plans to make Kobato
your official sister?"
and "How has your relationship
been progressing?" It was weird.
Sounds that way.
How did you answer him?
"Oh, I've got this!
Don't you worry!" Crap.
What?
So it seems he didn't realize
I was talking about Kobato.
He kinda thought I was
talking about you and me.
[KODAKA]
Are you serious?
If it helps, I feel
really bad about it.
Well, you cleared all that up
and explained everything to him,
didn't you?
Yeah.
That's good.
As long as he knows it was
just a big misunderstanding,
I'm sure it'll be fine.
[KODAKA] I kind of
feel bad for him,
but at least he knows the truth.
[SENA] So, uh-- Here's what
I wanted to talk about.
What?
There's more going on than that?
But for the record, this is
absolutely in no way my fault,
you got that?
Daddy only just told me about
this because of the crap drama
that's been going on
between us lately.
Okay.
Well he told me that um--
You and I are kind of engaged.
[SENA]
Are you all right?
Oh.
Yeah, uh huh.
[SENA] Daddy says back when we
were too young to remember,
he and your dad made
this promise to each other.
Basically, we're what
you'd call "betrothed".
[KODAKA]
Betrothed?
What are we like
a freakin' soap opera?
Might as well be since they also
decided they should write up
a marriage pact and
put our thumbprints on it.
Have you seen this pact?
I have!
Our little prints are pretty
adorable; they're so tiny!
What?
Really?
That's weird.
I don't remember that at all.
I didn't remember
either, but it's true.
Hold on.
Here, look.
[KODAKA]
It's us.
[SENA] Yep, it looks like we met
way before we thought we did.
[KODAKA]
How crazy.
Crazy.
That's the word for it.
I can't believe this.
Well, regardless,
it doesn't matter.
Nope.
I mean it's not like
we're gonna get married.
No way.
Not to mention the fact that
we shouldn't have to worry
about an engagement
we didn't make.
That would just be silly, right?
Yes, totally right.
Our dads are beyond random,
and that stuff has
nothing to do with us.
It's funny.
When it comes to my dad--
Well, knowing him the way I do
I seriously doubt that he
remembers this pact at all.
You think he won't?
Not even a little.
Trust me, there's no reason
for us to sweat this thing.
Well, okay, that's good news.
There's no reason
for us to sweat it.
Although that does
kind of make me sad.
I didn't say anything.
Besides, it doesn't really
matter if we're engaged.
I don't need you; I can make
Kobato my sister all by myself!
I don't suppose I can convince
you to give up on that, can I?
Whatever, let's go
back to the clubroom.
[SENA]
Look.
We may be fine, but--
I'm a little worried that
Slowzora will get all pissy
when she finds out about it.
Well, we don't have to
tell her about it, do we?
I mean, it doesn't
matter, anyway.
Yeah, I guess not.
Cool.
Let's go.
You're late!
What took so damn long?
Oh, nothing too important.
So are we gonna
go film now or what?
Yes, we are.
Okay, let's roll.
We can start with
the baseball field scene.
It's movie-making time!
Maria?
What?
I'm just excited!
I like making movies
with my big brother!
[MARIA]
♪ Movies, movies... ♪
Hm.
I have this weird feeling
like I'm forgetting something
really important.
But you do have Sena,
so well, that's out.
Hold on, if Kate thought
Sena and I were together.
I wonder if--
[MARIA]
Oh, right!
Are you and Sena
really gonna get married?
The stupid hag told me yesterday
that you guys were fiancées!
The word is fiancée, right?
I can't believe how grown up
you must be if you get to have
your very own fiancée;
you're gonna get married!
Married people are
grown up fiancées.
Um, what is she talking about?
[YOZORA]
They're betrothed.
And they met when they were
like, super little kids.
But it's no biggie!
What happened between our dads
back then has nothing to do
with us today!
Isn't that right?
That's right; yep,
that's totally right.
Rika.
I have a question.
Yes, Yozora.
How can Rika help you?
Do you think people who are
childhood friends or engaged
since before they can
remember are closer?
Rika believes most people
probably believe being betrothed
is indeed closer.
That's what I thought.
Although, I guess when
you think about how long
they've know each other,
one could consider them
childhood friends, as well.
That's what I thought.
Oh, come on; will you
get over yourself?
We're saying it doesn't matter,
so why are you
being so dramatic?
If you can't snap out of it
on your own, let me help!
Meat.
You're going to regret that.
Great.
Just wonderful.
Can we go film
something already?
Rika believes that Sena
has a good point, Yozora.
There's no point in worrying
about the promises our parents
might have made.
What's more important is
focusing on the here and now.
So where are we
supposed to film today?
[MARIA] I don't know, but
let's go make a movie!
Oh whatever.
I don't even care anymore.
[KODAKA]
Wait.
Big Brother!
Hey, Kotaro.
Uh, what is it?
It's Hironii, he--
He's in trouble,
and you've gotta help him!
Oh no!
[YOZORA]
Fine.
Cut.
How do you think it went?
Well.
[KODAKA]
She's not with us, is she?
We might as well move on
to the next scene for now.
Man, I'm so tired.
[KATE]
What's up, big bro?
Like you even care.
Today was a complete disaster,
and it was all thanks to you!
I'm sorry?
I can see why you're so upset,
and I do apologize.
But you should know we're
not the only ones who've
heard you and Sena are engaged.
I mean it's pretty much accepted
as a fact at this point.
Who--
Pegasus.
The guy talks about it
every chance he gets.
I'd say it's safe to assume
that all the faculty and
sisters here know about it.
I'd bet some students
think it's true, too.
Man, how can just one guy
have such a big mouth?
I'm sure he was
just excited, Kodaka.
How funny.
So Pegasus was
jumping to conclusions.
Huh?
What did you say?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Okay, let's move on
to something else.
I heard you guys are
making a movie, huh?
Uh huh.
What kind of movie
is it anyway?
I couldn't make heads
or tails outta what Maria
was trying to explain to me.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can believe that.
[KATE]
Oh, I see.
So it's a coming of age story
based on a transfer student.
The more you tell me about
it, the more it reminds me
of that film,
"Boys Over the Slope".
Really?
I've never even
heard of that before.
Yep.
It's another coming of age
movie that most people consider
a cult classic.
It's good.
I'm surprised you don't know it.
You should watch it
for research, at least.
Cool.
That sounds like
good reference material.
Great idea, Kate.
[BOY IN FILM]
Wait.
Big brother!
Hey, Kotaro.
What is it?
It's Hiro-nii, he--
He's in trouble, and
you've gotta help him!
[KODAKA]
No way.
Yozora.
How could she?
Why would she do
something like this?
She plagiarized
the entire script!
Okay, listen up.
I'll explain
exactly what happened.
I thought Sena and Kodaka were
dating, but that apparently
was not the case at all.
It may be hard
to accept as truth.
I know; I can barely
believe it myself.
No need to get upset;
let's stay calm.
You seem almost
happy about it, Kate.
No, no.
I'm not happy in the least!
Next time.
The Sad-Case King and
the Stone-Cold Story.
That Kodaka's got it rough, huh?
Maybe I have
a chance with him now.