[Music]
Mikazuki.
Here.
If I were you
I'd take a seat.
Yes, sir.
Sora?
It's been a while...
Taka.
This is the first time
we've really seen each
other in ten long years.
Which included France and
the Holy Roman Empire.
The Third Crusade was
the European attempt to
I remember that day he
first transferred here.
It was right around our
seasonal uniform change.
Hello...
I'm, uh...
The transfer student.
Okay... Great!
My name is Kodaka...
Nice to be... here!
Oh no, Miss Osada!
-Did he just attack her?
-Delinquent, much?
-He's new here?!
-What's up with his hair?
Taka...
It's Taka!
I'd recognize that hair
and expression anywhere.
It's definitely him!
He hasn't changed a bit
in the last ten years.
He always did
suck at smiling...
And the harder he tried to be
nice and friendly to people,
the more it would
just backfire on him.
I can't believe it.
I forgot my book.
Here! Take mine!
Oh, thanks...?
Yeah, that's him...
It's Taka.
My one and only friend
when I was a kid.
He didn't even notice me!
Well... Tell me what
you think, Tomo.
Yeah... Taka...
Or Kodaka Hasegawa...
My best friend from
back when I was a kid
who doesn't even remember
who I am now...
Isn't that the worst?!
Yeah...
My best guess is that
it's because I used
to dress like a boy
whenever we hung
out together...
And yeah I get that,
but still...
No way!
Why should I have be
the one to talk to him?
I mean, think about it...
I have no idea how to start a
conversation with somebody.
I don't know.
I thought maybe I could get
him to talk to me, first.
When I get to school.
When I leave the
class after school.
When I put things
in my locker.
Or take them back out.
I always have
to walk by him.
But he never says a
single word to me.
It's not like that at all!
Whaddaya mean
it's my fault?!
Right... Yeah...
and you know what, Tomo...
You make a really
good point.
Do you wanna go shopping
after school...?
I need some eyeliner.
Sure... Let's try that makeup
place across from the station.
I think I do remember...
No, I can't believe this...!
Crap... Kodaka saw me...!
Could he hear me talking?
I'm gonna die.
Please don't tell me he
heard what I was saying!
This is bad!
This is really bad!
What do I do?
What do you want?
I... I was just wondering.
Do you like, see
ghosts and stuff?
What...?
Uh, no...
'Cause ghosts don't exist.
Well then, who've
you been talking to?
You were watching me?
Look... I was having
a conversation
with my best friend ever...
She's made of air, okay!
And that was the
first conversation
I'd had with Taka
in ten years...
Also, I'm an idiot.
That's perfect...
A club!
See you later, Kodaka!
That's it...!
I'll start a club!
Here's a new club
application for ya'.
Thank you so much, sir.
If I'm not in a club...
I can make one!
A club just for
me and Kodaka!
Sometimes I
use this chapel
when I need a quiet
place to read...
or when the library's too
crowded for me to focus...
It's always
really comforting.
Sister Maria Takayama
is supposed to be in
charge of this room.
Apparently,
she's still a child.
I guess it's good
I don't hate kids.
Excuse me...
Hey! You!
Why the hell
are you in here?
This is my holy room for
napping, so get out...
It's not a place for
scummy sinners like you!
Hi, my name is
Yozora Mikazuki,
and I'm from
class two-five...
If you're Sister Maria,
I'm supposed to ask you...
Forget it.
What a little brat!
Okay...
I think if you just heard
me out, you'd see that...
I don't listen
to poopy heads.
Oh, you're gonna listen.
I'm applying to start a
new after school club.
And I was hoping
I could use this room.
No means no!
Now get out of here,
you grody plop of poop!
It's time!
Kodaka... Follow me, please.
Holy crap, she
talked to him.
To that Hasegawa creep?
Now... Let the clubbing begin!
Our purpose can be to
help us make friends...
Perfect, a club
for me and Kodaka...
Taka and Sora...
This way...
We'll be able to
become friends again
like we used to be.
Hey, Hasegawa!
Why is he staring
at Yozora like that?
They're still
standing-hello, awkward.
All right, moving on
with attendance.
-Miyajima.
-Here.
-Butou.
Yaegashi.
Yaegashi?
Sorry. Yeah, I'm here.
Good...
-Yamazaki.
-Here.
That's when I said...
So... um... Hey.
Hey what?
I was just...
What happened
to your hair?
Got it cut.
Yeah, well, I can
kinda see that...
But like...
why did you cut it?
Blame that summer
festival night.
But that was just
the tip, right?
It's not like the whole
thing got destroyed.
You didn't have
to cut off so much.
I did have to
cut this much off
because you totally
soaked my head.
No matter how many
times I washed my hair.
That freaking stench
would not come out!
Oh... I'm really sorry...
Please, I...
He soaked her head?
He said 'just the tip",
but did he force her?!
Yeah, that is not cool.
She washed and washed
but couldn't get the gross stink
of his stuff out of her hair.
You're wrong!
I was only doing
what had to be done!
Shut up and come on!
Wait! What?
Yozora!
Okay...
I, uh...
What I'm trying
to say is...
You're right, okay;
I was Sora...!
So what are you thinking?
I'm, uh...
Pretty surprised.
And anything else?
Like what?
You know, like else.
Like... Are you happy...?
Maybe honored...
Or are you moved at all?
How do I put it...
I'm bewildered by
the whole thing...
Surprised. Yeah,
that's definitely the
strongest feeling right now.
Oh.
That haircut does look
really good on you.
Thanks. You don't
think it's weird?
No... It's nice.
Oh...
Thank you.
I actually went
to a hair salon.
Wow... That must
have been fun...
Was it what you expected?
I was nervous.
Yeah, I can imagine
that you were.
Hold on a sec...
You knew who I was the
day I transferred here?
Yep... I knew from
the very beginning.
And I'm surprised
yet again.
Don't be. I'd recognize
your pudding head anywhere.
Thank you...
Well, you certainly
could've fooled me.
Wait...
But don't you
remember that day
when we met in the classroom?
I swear you said something
about not remembering
what my name was.
I was pretty irritated that
I recognized who you were,
even though you didn't
have a clue about me.
So you pretended you
didn't know me instead?
That's right.
Crap, we're at a dead end.
I'm sorry if I seemed rude.
But, I mean...
How can you blame
me for that?
It's not like...
I'd ever seen you wearing
a skirt... Right...?
You were only ever
dressed like a boy.
Who cares what I wore...
I never once told you I
was a boy when we were kids.
Sorry, it's just you don't
normally see girls
wearing boys clothes and
picking fights with other boys
whenever they could.
I was going to tell
you I was a girl,
but you up and disappeared
before I got the chance to.
Are you serious...?
That was the important thing
you said you were gonna tell me?
But you never showed
up that day...
And I waited...
A long time!
You're wrong...
Because I did
show up then...
But I got too embarrassed!
I was in a skirt...
and... and I was afraid
you would laugh at me.
You what?
I wore a skirt because
I wanted to confess to you
I was a girl.
I figured that was the
best way to let you know.
But, I'd never worn
a skirt before...
so I didn't know if it
looked good on me or not.
I thought maybe you
would laugh at me.
I just...
I couldn't make
myself do it...
It was way too
embarrassing...
But if I'd known
you were moving...
I might have gotten up the
courage to actually go for it.
You see! This whole
thing is all your fault!
There's no way!
Because, first
of all... weirdo...
you didn't have to wear
a skirt to tell me.
Whatever... You know for a
fact if I had just told you,
you never would've
believed me.
Yeah. You're probably right.
I think... Well...
The fact we
were friends...
I mean I think the fact
we were acquaintances
should remain a secret
from the rest of the club.
How come?
There's no reason
for them to know.
Uhh... Sure, that's fine.
Good, then that's that.
Okay, let's go.
One sec...
I don't know what
to call you now...
What do you
want me to use?
Yozora...
You can use my first name.
Don't you have a nickname or
something easier for me to say?
I do...
Did...
Look, I'm not going to
tell you what it was, Kodaka.
Why not?
Because only...
Only real friends use
nicknames with each other.
Hey, guys.
Oh, hello, Kodoka,
what's going on...
A double dose of
hotness with Kodaka
and a mystery stud muffin!
Ohmigah-ohmigah-ohmigah-te
ll Rika who this hot boy is,
tell her- tell her-tell her!
Tell you who this
hot boy is...
-Do you not see the skirt?
-No, wait.
Before you tell her who
this hottie boy delight is.
Rika will try to
deduce the answer.
Here she goes... He must be
your first younger friend!
Wrong.
So then your first older friend?
No.
Is he your
younger brother?
Don't have one.
Then he's your
older brother.
I don't have any brothers.
Huh...
He must be looking
at your soccer rival!
I have not and nor
will I ever play soccer.
Is he the president
of your student body?
I don't know
what that means.
Then tell me he's
your fiancée!
How do you come
up with these?
Alas... My Big Bro Kodaka
has left me for a stud muffin.
What the hell are you
talking about, Yukimura?!
This is hot...
Rika wonders which
one's the dominant
and which one's
the submissive...
Ooh... Does Kodaka like
to be the aggressive dom?
Or is he masochistically
submissive...?
Reluctant dom
or reluctant sub?
Rika bets it's hardcore
no matter what they do!
Oh just imagining
it makes Rika all...
She's such a freak job.
Get it together...
This is just...
Hey! Yozora...
You got your hair cut.
Well... Yeah...
Thank you,
Captain Obvious.
Oh... Yozora...
What's up?
Who?
Yozora... It's you.
That's right...
I am still me.
You chopped a ton of
your hair off, lady.
So... What'd you do it for?
It doesn't have anything
to do with you Meat.
Oh, come on.
Why not just tell me?
It won't cost
you anything.
Nothing except
for my precious time.
What? Are you saying
that talking to me
is a waste of time?!
-You said it, sister, not me.
-And things are back to normal.
You! Stay right here
until Rika's back!
What's she up to, now?
Now then... Did you cut it
because of a broken heart?
-Shut up.
-Yes...! That's it, right...?
You totally just
lost a lover!
Awesome!
I said shut up!
Poor mean old Yozora had
love ripped away from her...!
I wonder why?!
So, spill it, who is
this lucky fella anyway?
Whoever it is deserves
a medal for realizing
what a massive tool you are
and kicking you to the curb.
How could you hit my face?
That's sacred!
I do not have a broken
heart, you idiot...
However...
Now I know how
you would react
if I did get my heart broken
which helps to prove
how awful you truly are.
Well, that sucks...
I thought I'd finally get
the chance to bully her,
but I guess not...
If your heart hasn't
been stomped on,
then why did you cut it.
You don't get
to know that.
Oh, come on...! Tell me!
Okay, Yozora!
Will you please
try this on?
What is that...?
Is it like a dance
uniform from somewhere?
You're exactly right! Yeah!
This is an original,
legitimate white uniform coat
officially worn by the
student council president...
Of the one and only
Galford Academy!
Of Galford... Academy?
Yes, and for
real, Yozora...
Rika knows this is gonna
look amazing on you!
But... isn't this...
just like a cosplay
uniform thing?
Why would I want to
dress up in costume
in the middle of the day?
'Cause... It'll look amazing.
Rika already said so!
Hey, Big Brother!
It's so good to see you!
Wow, someone's sure
in a good mood today.
Why are you standing
out in the hallway...
Oh... You were caught being
naughty again weren't you?
Uh, just what do
you mean by again?
Okay guys, come in!
What did Rika say?
Amazing, right?
Yeah... She looks...
Agh...!
There's a hot guy...!
There's a really
hot guy in here!
Why are you so
scared, Maria?
Because, everyone knows
hot guys chew up and spit out
cute little girls like me!
That's what all the
other sisters say,
and I don't want
to be gnawed on
just because I'm
this adorable!
Hey... Cutey...
I'm gonna munch on you.
I don't taste good at all,
so please leave me alone!
Go away!
I'm going to munch you...
'kay...
And then I'm
going to crunch.
Didn't we go through this
exact same thing already?
Kodaka...
About my summer homework, I...
Take her...!
If you're gonna eat anybody,
it should be a vampire!
She'll taste better
than me, I swear it!
-You're gonna eat me?
-No...
Um... No one's eating you.
I will...!
I'll eat Kobato into little
pieces; let me have at her!
Hey! What was that for?!
You should be ashamed
of yourself, meatwad...
You have serious issues.
Oh great...
She shows up after
disappearing for a week...
And even though she
has a whole new look,
Yozora is still just Yozora.
You better believe it...
Why would I ever
want to change...?
I'm perfect the way I am.
I don't know what
to call you now.
What do you
want me to use?
Sora?
Call me by my name... Yozora.
Like you've been doing.
That sound good...
Kodaka?
Sounds good...
Yozora.
Great.
Yozora and I...
Well, No, I guess Sora and
Taka used to be best friends.
But now... Yozora Mikazuki
and Kodaka Hasegawa aren't.
I know that
Yozora was Sora...
But we can't
just pick up
where we left off ten
years ago, can we?
I wonder...
What will happen
to us after this?
Okay, at least tell
me why so short!
I don't have to tell you
why I do what I do to my hair!
I don't really
know the answer...
I hope to someday...
I think, though...
That's why I should stick
around here for a while.
You're a poopy vampire,
what do you know?
Horrid disciple of God!
Here in this club,
where all we're trying
to do is make some friends.
[Music]
Now... It's time to begin
the Neighbors Club activities
for the new term!
[Music]
HYou let your guard a
previdown too easily...sode?
We're having an
extra episode.
Why? So what's it
gonna be about?
That's a secret!
-Tell me!
-Okie-dokie!
So! It's not a secret!!
It's legendary...
An episode banned
from television
and never before
revealed to anyone!
I didn't realize we
had one of those.
And the epic title is...
A Round Robin Story's
Ending Is Way Extreme!
There she goes.
The round-robin story: the
door to a forbidden world!