Hey.
I--
Nice, just who I wanted to see!
What's up?
Oh.
Hey, how's it going, Rika?
Rika does not appreciate
your crappy tone!
I don't think I've ever seen you
without your glasses before.
Rika thought it'd be fun
to do something
different for a change.
Maybe Rika should
dye her hair next!
[KODAKA]
You're wearing contacts now?
Actually, Rika doesn't
need to wear glasses at all!
That's right,
Rika's vision is perfect!
If you don't have to wear them,
then what's the point?
Rika is being fashionable,
isn't it obvious?
Did the word
"fashionable" seriously come
out of your mouth?
How about "character design?"
Oh yeah, that sounds
more up your alley.
Despite what you think,
Rika's more than some
nerdy scientist
stuck in a lab all day.
So, surely you now find
Rika sexier than ever!
[KODAKA] Who knew such a sex
fiend could come across as naïve
and innocent by simply
taking off her glasses?
As for whether
I'd hit that or not,
I'd have to say--Hellz yeah.
You could show some restraint.
Rika's sitting right here.
[KODAKA] Wait a second,
I actually said that out loud?
Yeah, ya dummy!
What did you do that for?
Beats me.
[SENA]
Ugh. Rot in Hell.
[YUKIMURA]
How primal.
[KODAKA] When did the
rest of you get here?
Well, aren't you a dirty boy!
[RIKA laughing]
Rika never knew you
harbored such lustful desire
for her supple body!
Force Rika onto this table
and take her from behind!
[KODAKA]
Shut up!
Oh my, perhaps Rika should
speak with more eloquence.
A touch of class is
the way to a man's heart!
Would you please
rip off Rika's clothes
and give her your sweet manhood?
How was that a touch of class?
Man, of all people
you just had to be Rika.
Is desiring Rika so painful?
Observe the tears
welling up in her eyes.
Well, I guess I'd better
start hitting the books.
He dares to pour salt into the
open wound of Rika's heart!
Though Rika must admit.
As much as it hurts,
it also feels good.
Rika is dripping wet!
[trickling water]
Have it your way.
Rika will once again retreat
from her cruel reality
and escape to a better world.
[RIKA]
Hey Sena.
May Rika please use the TV?
Oh yeah, sure.
What game are you gonna play?
[RIKA]
It's not a game.
Rika's going to
watch Homo Game Club!
It arrived in
the mail just yester--.
Seriously, what makes you think
we'd let you watch
that garbage in here?
[RIKA]
Homo Game Club isn't garbage!
The title may be kinda weird,
and the game it's based on is
only for players who're
eighteen and up, but all
the naughtier parts have been
watered down for the movie.
They wanted to make sure
kids could watch it, too.
Heck, even your
grandma would like it.
All the steamy love scenes
have been replaced with
more subtle hotness.
So now it's not as explicit and
appeals to a broader audience!
Big deal, who wants to
watch two dudes snuggle up?
Rika loves watching
men get busy!
How could you not stare
at this cover for hours?
Get that thing out of
my face right now.
[RIKA] See? I told you
it's not a porno.
Fine, it's not porn.
But any movie with that creepy
a title and three naked dudes
side by side on the cover
is bound to be messed up.
Rika doesn't think you should
simply judge a book by its cover
without taking
a look at what's inside.
She's right, people always
jump to conclusions about stuff
they know nothing about.
Rika knew you'd agree!
Try to get to know
something before you start
throwing around assumptions.
It sucks to be judged
just by how you look.
It sucks hardcore.
Um.
Yeah, go ahead and
stick in the movie.
Way to get Yozora
to change her mind!
As for you, get ready to feast
your eyes on PG-rated manlove!
This basically rehashes
the TV show with a few
minor tweaks here and there.
You should be able to follow
along without a problem.
♪
[RIKA giggling excitedly]
Wanna play with me?
[FUMIO]
What?
No!
You'll never catch me
playing that kinky stuff!
A fan-made game, huh?
I'm all ears, bro.
Are we gonna do this?
Together?
[FUMIO]
You can count on me!
[MISAO]
Dammit!
Not a one.
We sold zero copies!
Damn it all to hell!
Shut up!
We're in this for
more than just sales,
we're in it for ourselves!
[evil laughter]
Homo Game Club,
you're finished!
Finished forever!
[evil laughter]
You'll have to get past my
rock-hard six-pack!
[KODAKA]
You're blocking the TV.
No matter the cost,
even if the entire world's
against the two of us.
I'll never stop
protecting you, Fumio.
Dummy.
You know that's my line.
I'll be right by your side,
now and forever!
It's pretty touching stuff,
wouldn't ya say?
Uh, sure, I suppose it is.
It takes a lot of courage
to open up like that.
But your secret's safe with me.
I promise.
Thank you.
[RIKA swooning]
[MEN passionately moaning,
KODAKA gagging]
♪
[sighing]
The best two hours
of Rika's young life!
I'm just so happy
I finally got to see it.
[YOZORA]
Rika?
Yeah?
[YOZORA] Why did Fumio and
Koyomi-- uh, you know--
why'd they kiss at the end?
Wait, for realz, yo?
When emotions are running high
in the heat of the moment,
people always kiss!
What?
But still, those two
guys were best friends,
and I thought
friends couldn't kiss.
Of course they can.
Human impulse
knows no boundaries!
Well, even so.
Isn't that a little weird?
Kissing one of your friends
just-- it seems wrong.
What are you talking about?
When two people feel the magic
of romantical chemistry,
the next step's to
kiss lips, spread legs,
and scream till
the neighbors come!
It don't matter if they're
best friends, it don't matter
if they're two dudes,
what matters is they best be
gettin' busy under the sheets!
Two naked men going at it.
Rika thanks God for
this precious gift!
Maybe you should stick to your
dirty robot comics from now on.
I see.
Even friends kiss each other
when the time is right.
I will admit,
I should never have judged
Homo Game Club that way.
Awesomeness!
Does this mean you'll join Rika
as a member of the
Homo Game Club Fan Club?
Uh.
I'll have to get back
to you on that one.
Right now, I'll just say
it was better than I expected.
That's all.
Rika's ecstatic that
you enjoyed it so much!
And if you've got
any other good stuff,
feel free to
bring it up to the club.
On it!
Finally, Rika's got
her first friend!
But this friendship
might not last if Rika
can't produce another movie!
Think hard Rika,
what's another fun one?
"My Baby Maker Can't Be
This Cute" is another
homoerotic masterpiece,
but it's out of print.
And "Squid or Octopus:
Don't Make Me Choose" goes
right for the tentacle rape.
[SENA]
This is so unfair!
What's wrong now, Meat?
[SENA]
Don't act like you don't know!
You're always slamming my
dating games and calling them
creepy as hell.
What makes Rika's
gay shows any better?
Homo Game Club is about the
importance of true friendship,
a theme that's
relevant to this club.
Don't compare it to the
ridiculous filth that's
on your computer
twenty-four-seven.
There's no comparison.
Hey, you haven't even played
one yet, so how would you know?
If your dumb games
are so appropriate,
then try reading one of
the scenes out loud for us.
[YOZORA] Why don't you do
the one you're on right now?
Judging by your expression,
you can't wait to share it.
[SENA]
Um, this particular scene
isn't the most accurate
representation of the game.
That doesn't matter,
I could read any scene out of
Homo Game Club out loud
and it'd still seem normal.
There's a lot more to it
than just getting reamed
in the forest!
All right then,
go ahead and try it!
Oh, I remember this part.
I'm ready, hit play.
[BOTH] No matter the cost, even
if the entire world's against
the two of us, I'll never
stop protecting you, Fumio.
[BOTH] You dummy,
you know that's my line.
There's nothing that we
can't conquer as long as
we have each other!
[SENA] That was the ending;
of course it sounds
cool and dramatic!
Let's try out
a different scene. This one.
[BOTH] Ain't no one gonna break
my stride and ain't no one
gonna slow me down.
I've got to keep on moving no
matter what stands in my way!
Bah!
Really?
There've got to be
crappy-sounding lines
somewhere in this movie!
Nah, they took all the best
scenes from the TV show,
remember?
[BOTH] Don't ever be ashamed of
who you really are inside.
Everyone will
have their doubters,
but you can't let anyone
else decide who you are.
No!
Not another cool one!
Who knew guys could be
such smooth talkers?
Don't underestimate Misao.
How did she already
memorize the entire movie?
[YOZORA] Now then, I think I've
proven my point well enough.
Your turn.
Let me hear a scene from
one of your dating games.
What's wrong, sandbags?
If there's nothing
to be ashamed of,
then you've got
nothing to be afraid of.
The dialogue in this
scene should do nicely!
Whenever you're ready!
Go on.
Do it.
Now!
[screaming]
Fine, no big deal.
It's just like the movie!
It's not like there's gonna
be anything remotely dirty.
Besides, a girl ought
to be able to say whatever
she likes without having
catty people judge her!
By the time I'm through,
I'll prove to you that
"One Day I Suddenly Got a Blonde
Little Sister with Pigtails
and I Can't Take It
Anymore" is a work of art.
Maybe even a masterpiece!
Is that really the title?
Okay.
Here we go.
[nervously] Big brother, gimme
your big, juicy, thick--
What?
Big, brother, gimme your
big juice-- juicy, uh.
Your, um.
Thick.
Louder, clearer,
and more feeling!
How about using some emotion?
[inhaling]
[screaming] Big brother, I want
you to give me your big, juicy,
thick [BEEP] and
drench me with your hot,
sticky [BEEP] until
I'm gasping for air!
There, I [BEEP]ing said it!
Wow.
She really did it.
Did you think you were going to
win every single
battle against me?
Gotta hand it to you, Meat,
I never thought you'd say that.
Yeah?
Too bad!
Don't underestimate me!
More importantly,
I've proved that my dating games
aren't embarrassing at all!
Oh.
Okay.
Mhm, I guess you kinda
beat me this time.
Wha--?
At least look at
my face when you admit it!
Rika's jealous that even
her supercharged libido
can't match up with yours.
That was impressive, Sena.
I had no clue you were oozing
with so much sexual energy.
Yeah, no kidding,
who would've thought.
I certainly have a better
understanding of why your
gaming habits are what they are.
So I'm sorry for
making fun of you.
You're all a bunch
of dumb perverts!
Screw you!
[door slamming,
SENA crying]
Well, here's to finally
being done with finals.
[SISTER burping]
[SISTER] Hey, you there,
with the freaky hairdo!
Come on, turn around
my little lamb.
Don't leave a sister hangin'!
Turning your back on a servant
of God like me is basically
buying yourself
a one-way ticket to Hell!
I'm sorry.
But are you by any
chance talking to me?
[SISTER] Well naturally!
Who else has got
hair like that?
Oopsy daisy.
Who says "Oopsy daisy?"
What do you want from me?
Just figured I'd let
ya know that if you
need anyone to talk to,
I'm open ears.
It's a sister's duty.
Well, I guess I do
have my share of problems.
I can tell!
Life's been coming
at you fast, am I right?
Some people will even
mess with their appearance
to deal with the stress!
Sorry, but if you're
referring to my hair,
that's actually
its natural color.
What?
That's natural?
Oh.
Who woulda thunk it?
Yep, no one ever said
hard living was easy!
[KODAKA]
What does that mean?
I gotta run, but it
was nice meeting you.
Yeah, if you have any issues,
just swing by the counseling
center and hit me up.
The name's Kate Takayama, 'kay?
Some kids call me "Mother Kate"
since a lot of them
are younger than me.
Takayama?
[MARIA]
Big brother!
I've finally found you!
You can't get away from me!
Hey, that girl over there.
Do you know her?
Get away from big brother
right now, you poopy old hag!
I guess I'll take that as a yes.
Maria!
Keep it up kiddo, I dare ya!
[MARIA]
Oww, quit it, stupidface!
I'll kill you!
What, don't you remember what
you're supposed to call me?
You dummy fart freckles idiot!
Fartfreckles, now there's
an impressive vocabulary!
[MARIA]
Die!
Die, poopy butt!
Pooper trooper!
Hurry up and say it, kid!
"I love you, big sis."
[MARIA]
Ow ow ow ow ow, it hurts!
Stop it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Please let go!
Forgive me!
I love you, big sister poop!
Keep em coming, you brat!
[MARIA] I'm sorry, big sis,
for real this time!
So you must be
Kodaka Hasegawa, am I right?
[KODAKA]
Oh. Yeah.
[KATE]
That's cool.
My little sis talks
about you a lot, like nonstop.
Little sister?
[KATE]
Yep!
I'm Maria's older sister.
Nice to meet ya!
Man, it does feel kinda weird,
seeing her Big Brother Kodaka
for the first time
and everything.
Maria's an idiot,
in case you haven't noticed.
So please look
after her for me, okay?
[MARIA]
You're the idiot!
Big brother hangs out
with me because he likes me,
not because your
stupid face tells him to!
Hag!
Hey!
You better get
all your chores done!
[MARIA]
Don't wanna, poopy-head!
What a pain.
Seriously, how can someone
so idiotic be related to me?
[burping]
It sucks!
But I am grateful for your help.
Yours and everyone else's in
that group you hang out with.
And which group is that?
[KATE] You call it the
Neighbors Club, right?
Maria's been in a
better mood ever since
she became the club's advisor.
[KODAKA]
Oh, is that right?
I figured she had always
been pretty optimistic.
Actually the opposite.
Long story short,
she feels a lot more comfortable
in the classroom
than outside of it.
She's real cocky about her
grades so she has trouble
making friends.
And it's gotten worse since
she started skipping ahead.
So, it's good she has you to
hang out with when she's lonely.
Your little sister as well.
The chick vampire.
Oh, and also Yozora Mikazuki.
I basically owe that girl
a thank you card.
Wait, for Yozora?
[KATE] We were way too easy on
Maria when she was younger,
and we kind of
ended up spoiling her.
But Yozora is willing
to deal with her attitude
and not let her have
her way every single time.
She treats Maria like a kid
instead of a prodigy or genius.
That's probably
a lot better for her.
Having someone she can't
just look down on to get
what she wants takes her
out of her comfort zone.
[KODAKA]
Can't say I saw that one coming.
Props, Yozora!
Could you do a big favor for me,
though, and get Maria to quit
flashing people
in broad daylight?
[KODAKA]
Of course!
I'll talk to her about that.
Good!
Other than that, thanks
again for looking after her.
Thank you, Big Brother!
Right.
Did you say big brother?
You're Maria's
big brother, aren't you?
So by default you're
like my big brother, too!
I mean I'm fifteen,
so you're older.
Welp, see ya, bro!
[farting]
That's a wet one!
[YOZORA]
Kodaka!
I kinda figured you'd
be at the clubroom by now.
Nah.
someone held me up for a while.
Somebody I know?
By the way, Kodaka.
Yeah?
Did you finish all
your final exams, too?
Yep.
I read about this thing friends
supposedly do after tests.
They get together and compare
answers and see who got
what for which questions.
Ah, yeah, I guess that's a
friendly-sounding sort of thing
to do afterwards.
Yeah, it's pretty stupid.
I mean, it's not like your
grade's gonna get any better.
But that being said,
when we've got friends
of our own to talk to, I'm sure
we'll be forced into doing
the whole compare answers thing,
whether we like it or not.
Sure, it's possible.
So yeah, I think--
Well, I think we should probably
start practicing for the future!
You do see what
I'm getting at, right?
Yeah, okay.
Let's start!
Ok!
What was your answer
for the fourth question of
the third section
on the Math Two exam?
For the Math test?
But we took that
one on the first day!
How am I supposed to
remember the answers when
I can't remember the question?
This is exactly what
I was afraid would
happen our first time.
What kind of question was it?
It was one of those math proofs
worth a decent chunk of credit.
Oh, that one, yeah!
My answer ended up
being really long.
I don't feel great about it.
Wait.
How are we supposed to share
answers when we don't have
the tests in front
of us to compare?
Yeah, I guess that is
a pretty good point.
I think we're better off just
saying, "That one was tough".
or "I'm pretty sure I got it"
before we actually try to answer
and do complicated things.
We are still just practicing.
Okay.
Hey buddy, that question was
a toughie, don'tcha think?
Yeah!
Yeah, it sure was!
Alright, we gotta do it with
a different type of question!
Definitely, maybe like
a multiple choice
or fill-in-the-blank one!
Better yet, something
from today's exam!
There was one today
that had me stumped.
The eleventh blank in
Section Two of the History exam.
[KODAKA]
Gimme a sec.
Let me see.
"After Hojo Tokimune's death,
vassal Adachi Yasumori was
overthrown by inner
Administrator blank
number eleven."
It's obviously Taira Yoritsuna,
so I put him down.
Yeah, I doubt too many people
got that question wrong.
However, I think I may've
misspelled the name Yoritsuna,
like with one letter off.
I better not get docked
a lot of points for that.
[KODAKA] She wouldn't
grade us that harshly!
Yoritsuna or Yoritsuno.
One letter spells the
difference between passing
and flunking out of school.
That's the most
random mistake ever.
Then again.
You could've misspelled it, too!
Or maybe you botched the
whole thing and you're screwed
for the rest of your life!
Now you've got me worried
about it, I hope you're happy!
No, I must've put
Yoritsuna, didn't I?
We'll find out soon enough.
I felt pretty good about myself
till you opened your damn mouth.
Comparing answers
is freaking stressful!
You got that one right!
Okay then, why don't we
move on to the next one?
Number Eighteen in Section Two.
Okay.
"In Year 1 of the Shochu Era,
blank number Eighteen."
Yeah, I took a random
guess on this one.
[SENA]
The year thirteen twenty-four!
Oh hey, how's it going, Sena.
What are you two doing?
Comparing answers?
Uh-huh.
That's awesome, then I'll grace
you both with my knowledge!
You guys are lucky,
it's not often that I tutor
the less fortunate!
What can I say, I'm generous!
Beat it breasticles,
we don't need you.
Bitch, what's your problem?
I've got all the
answers down pat!
Math Two, Section Three,
Question Five, answer now.
That one was the
square root of five!
[KODAKA] How are they memorizing
all the questions by number?
Japanese, Section Two,
Question One, part three!
The irregular conjugation!
What?
Man, I said it was
the infinitive.
[KODAKA]
Better luck next time, Yozora.
[SENA]
Come on, come on.
Ask me another one!
Buzz off.
Comparing answers is a stupid
waste of time, anyway.
It's not like it's gonna bump
your grade up or anything.
[KODAKA]
Here we go.
[SENA]
Hold on a sec!
Wait!
Just give me one more question!
I don't care how hard it is,
it can be anything you want.
[YOZORA]
No.
Comparing answers with Meat
is dumb and serves no purpose.
But-- Don't tell me that;
Tamama who sat next to me
in eighth grade told
me the same thing!
Please, I'd rather compare
answers with Tomo than with you.
Speaking of-- Hey, Tomo,
what did you put down for
Question Seven
on the Bio exam?
[SENA]
Jerk!
Quit mumbling crazy talk to
yourself when I'm right -- Oh!
The answer to that was
Calvin-Benson Cycle!
[YOZORA] I wasn't sure, but
I put Calvin-Benson Cycle.
Really, you put that down too?
Then I bet we got it right!
You're so awesome, Tomo!
[SENA]
Quit ignoring me, you douchebag!
Phew, we're finally
through with final exams!
I hit the books
harder than usual this year,
but they were
still pretty rough.
Our school had finals after
summer vacation because
it's on the two-term system.
The more you know, am I right?
Are you talking to Tomo again?
Anyway, we're not gonna have
any more tests for a while.
Yeah!
Now there's plenty
of time to study for
the next batch of tests!
Don't be a downer!
Next Time on Haganai NEXT: "My
Little Sisters Are This Cute."
Kodaka, you really have
a thing for your little sis?