[students whispering]
[MALE STUDENT 1] He looks
so pissed off right now.
[MALE STUDENT 2] Yeah,
like ready to punch pissed.
[FEMALE STUDENT 1]
I hate it when he comes here.
[FEMALE STUDENT 2]
He so freaks me out.
[students gasping]
[KODAKA]
Here we go again.
Same old, same old.
Same old attitudes about me.
Same old after school whatever.
Same old Neighbors Club.
Hey, guys.
Sorry about that.
Wrong room.
Hey, get back here, Kodaka!
Don't you like my hair?
Totally.
Yeah, it looks great on you.
Well, thanks.
I mean, no!
I'm asking you if
you think it's funny!
If it's funny?
Obvi.
Don't you remember yesterday
we were talking about
making friends by being
funny and entertaining?
I remember.
So, you did this?
The sign at the toy store said
this thing was guaranteed
to be a hit, so I bought it.
[KODAKA] You take this
stuff too seriously.
[YOZORA]
I couldn't agree more.
As I suspected,
the distinguished art form
known as comedy is well
beyond Meat's capacity.
Oh come on; not you, too.
Today, I'm dressed up as one of
the most laughable creatures
ever to exist.
Tell the truth; you know
I'm hilarious right now.
Okay, then how about this?
You hooker!
I'm gonna murder you.
Woe is me; I'm just so like
rich and pretty and like oh no.
[SENA] You're so stupid;
I don't sound like that!
You're right I like
so don't sound like that,
I sound more like this.
Oh, look at me;
I need attention...
I am not a laughable
creature, you big jerk!
Besides, you're
not even funny;
you're just
annoying like normal.
That's awesome.
Welcome to my world; now you can
see how much fun your crying
and bitching is
for the rest of us.
Shut up.
You're awful.
[KODAKA]
Hey, Yozora?
I'm surprised you're not
embarrassed to look that way.
Anyway.
You know, girls, true comedy is
more than just cheap gimmicks.
No one who looks like you
gets to be condescending.
Yeah.
Since you know so much,
why don't you show us
this mystical "true comedy"?
Oh, I can do that.
True comedy...
...now listen up...
...is about talking.
[BOTH]
Talking?
That's what I said.
Now, get ready to
laugh your faces off.
So here we go.
Two nuns walk into a bar.
And then the priest said,
"Bless you my child."
And the bartender said,
"Yeah, that's what she said."
Get it?
[BOTH]
So lame.
[RIKA]
Comedy, huh?
Rika agrees popular
people do have a tendency
to be rather funny.
Big Brother.
Here is your tea.
Thanks.
I wish I had been around to
hear you tell your funny story.
Was it great?
[SENA]
No. Count your blessings.
Truth.
It was way beyond bad.
Hey!
Well.
At least I did more than just
change my stupid hairstyle
like you guys did.
Hush.
No one asked you.
Oh, speaking of hairstyles,
I recently heard something
pretty fascinating.
What did you hear?
[YOZORA] I read a magazine that
said this style called a "pouf"
is really popular right now.
You know, for people
with actual lives.
A pouf?
Well, you literally pouf up
your hair to make it all big.
And after you've got that
crazy volume, you're supposed
to put random decorations
and stuff in it.
Weird.
But it does kinda sound fun.
[RIKA] Rika's seen pictures of
that all over the internet.
They almost remind Rika of
medieval European nobility.
Seriously?
Sounds like it's perfect for me!
There are historically
super extreme versions
of the pouf, too.
Like they'd twist their hair up
into an elaborate cage and
then put a real, live bird in
there and get it to flap around.
For real.
Why would they do that?
Rika supposes they wanted
to emphasize individuality
over functionality,
a concept not unlike that of
the Warring States helmets.
So, basically, this "pouf"
style, like the helmets
of the warring state generals,
was designed to serve as proof
of identity for those brave
souls who were tragically
beheaded in battle.
That way, their heads
would receive the respect
deemed appropriate for their
position, not to mention...
That is in no way accurate.
That's a real shame.
Okay.
I mean, I don't totally get it,
but I'll assume you guys do.
If you ask me, only like
a really exceptional person
would have the ability
to pull off this look.
A boring old commoner would look
ridiculous if they even tried,
am I right?
Sorry if I'm annoying
you with all this talk
of something
irrelevant to your life.
Anyways, the safest bet for
an ordinary commoner would be
to get an ordinary hairdo
at an ordinary salon.
Still, though, one day
I hope I get the chance to see
a pouf in real life.
Rika does too,
but it would be difficult.
There just aren't many people
out there with the naturally
aristocratic and gorgeous aura
needed to carry such a look.
That class of intense
self-assuredness
is so hard to come by.
Preach, sister.
What a crying shame.
[KODAKA]
They couldn't be more obvious.
I could pull off a pouf!
[KODAKA]
It worked.
I'm an aristocrat who's like
overflowing with awesome aura;
no one is better suited
for the pouf than me!
Don't strain yourself, Meat.
She's right, Sena; the pouf is
an exceedingly tricky hairstyle,
and we don't want you to
accidentally hurt yourself.
I'm not gonna get hurt!
The aura of divinity
I project from within is enough
to carry off anything,
much less some silly, little,
fad hairstyle.
[KODAKA] And this is why
she's such an easy target.
Okay, well, if you're up for it,
I don't mind poofing your hair
for you right this minute.
Good idea.
Rika has all sorts of tools in
her lab and will go get them!
Tools.
What for?
Kay.
We're both ready if you are!
I'm ready; just don't
go too crazy, okay?
[YOZORA]
Quit squirming, Meat.
This is gonna be fun.
Well, I have to admit,
it's pretty nice to have another
girl brush your hair for you.
Oh wow.
Rika can't believe how shiny
and smooth your hair is, Sena.
Rika can't see
a single split end.
Guess I can give you credit for
good hair, too, if nothing else.
[SENA]
Thanks!
[RIKA] Yozora, your hair
is also very pretty.
Rika's way jealous.
I guess it's not horrible,
which makes it her one
redeeming characteristic.
But don't sell yourself short,
Rika, because your
hair is awesome.
[YOZORA]
I told you not to move.
[RIKA]
Is it really?
[YUKIMURA]
Here, a refill.
Thank you.
[YOZORA]
All right, it's poofing time.
Any requests, Meat?
Oh, I dunno.
You could try to make me
look like someone
who has a real life.
[YOZORA]
A "has a life" theme, huh?
Real lives make me
think of... summer?
Yeah, that's perfect.
We can give it a whole
"girl who has a real life
enjoying summer" feel.
First, let's wave the sides
to evoke the image
of rolling ocean waves!
Yes. I like it.
Next, why don't we try putting
in sassy little ringlets
that'll represent
the swirling tides!
[RIKA] And this part
can be a summer storm,
so kind of flashy frizz!
What do you think of it, Sena?
I, uh.
Yeah, that works.
[YOZORA]
Now for the top.
Since the sides are the ocean,
the top should be a
sandcastle on the beach!
How about we use a real bikini
instead of plain ol' ribbons?
Oh yeah, and a watermelon
and some fireworks
to complete the picture.
A bikini?
And watermelon?
And why not some yakisoba
while we're at it, right?
Totes right.
You're a genius.
[SENA]
Well, I think--
[BOTH]
Will you stop moving?
I'll go right now and purchase
a bikini, a watermelon,
and some yakisoba!
[YOZORA]
Thanks, bro!
Okay, what do you
think about this, here?
[SENA]
Kodaka, help me.
[KODAKA]
Sorry.
There's nothing I can do.
[MARIA]
Poke.
Poke, poke, poke.
Fly.
Go on, fly.
[YUKIMURA]
Excuse me.
[MARIA]
I'm doing it!
I promise!
Look, I'm doing it just
like I'm supposed to!
Oh, hey, Yukimura.
Hello, Sister Maria.
What are you doing out here?
[MARIA]
What does it look like?
The old hags are forcing me
into hard labor as punishment
for slacking off.
So, that's my story.
What are you doing?
Well, all the girls in the club.
Blah, blah, blah, and so forth.
[MARIA] I have a bunch
of summery things!
Look at these!
You can totally
take them with you!
[YOZORA AND RIKA]
All done!
Okay.
It's called the
"Ultimate-Satisfying-Social-
Life-Meets-Midsummer-Night's-
Dream Mega Pouf"!
OMG, Sena, you
look super adorbs.
[KODAKA]
Wow. That is not right.
[YOZORA]
I can't get over the gorgeous.
[YUKIMURA] Your head would make
a most magnificent war trophy.
Thanks, guys.
It really looks that good?
Really.
It's beautiful!
Wow, your hair's
not simply gaudy.
It's also poignant
and inspirational.
I gotta say, I agree.
And I'm jealous.
I wish I'd tried a pouf
before I cut all my hair off.
[SENA]
Yeah, I think it's a winner.
I love it!
[KODAKA]
They've all lost their minds.
What do you think
of my pouf, Kodaka?
Um.
It expresses the
group aesthetic.
I mean, like right?
Okay, bye guys!
I'm going home, now!
I hope she'll be all right.
[SENA WHINING]
Kodaka!
Oh.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Get this.
Daddy was so mad at me
when I got home yesterday,
like raging mad.
[SENA CRYING]
He spanked me hard, and he made
me put my hair back to normal.
It was the worst thing ever.
Wow, that blows.
[KODAKA]
All right, Pegasus.
Good job.
Yesterday, Rika might've gotten
a little too carried away.
But now that she's calmed down,
she realizes it was wrong.
Yeah, I did the same thing.
We're very sorry, Meat.
Why couldn't you guys at least
let this be a funny ending?
Stupid!
[SENA CRYING]
[KODAKA] And so, the club
meeting ended in disappointment.
[PHONE]
You've got mail.
I guess I should go.
I see how it is.
Hey, what's up?
[KOBATO]
Kodaka! You gotta help me!
[SENA]
Kobato, come back!
Where are you going?
[KOBATO]
No! Get away from me! Help!
What the hell is
going on over there?
[STUDENTS] Did you hear that
scream over the phone, too?
Think someone was kidnapped?
[KOBATO SCREAMING]
[STUDENTS FREAKING OUT]
No.
Everyone's fine.
[PHONE]
You've got mail.
[KODAKA] I heard Sena's got
the best GPA in our grade.
[KODAKA] Kobato, I'm gonna
study out at Sena's place
for a while this
afternoon, okay?
[KOBATO] Kay.
I don't suppose you'd want
to come along with me?
[KOBATO gasping]
What's wrong?
My dearest other half
and brother.
I bid you take care.
So in other words,
you don't wanna go.
No, I don't.
She scares me.
True enough.
[KODAKA] Wow, Sena,
she really hates you.
Good afternoon.
Welcome back.
Hey, Kodaka.
You're here!
Indeed he is, which
makes it time to study.
[SENA]
Really?
You mean you're done
with him already?
[PEGASUS]
I am.
So, what was that about?
[SENA]
Oh.
Daddy's always
asking about you,
so I figured he'd
want some time with you.
Like, maybe he'd want to talk
to you himself this time.
What?
Sena!
I am not always
asking about Kodaka!
Yes.
Well, Hayato called and
asked me to look after you.
So naturally I'm
concerned for your welfare.
[KODAKA] I don't know
if I'll ever get that guy.
[SENA]
All right, Kodaka!
Let's go get our
study on in my room!
[SENA]
Here it is.
It's okay to come in.
Right.
Cool.
Walk through the door.
Wait, uh--.
Whoa.
That's messed up.
They're great pictures, right?
That jerk, like,
never lets her guard down,
so it took me
forever to get them.
Um, this seems healthy to you?
Yeah.
Why wouldn't it be, silly?
[KODAKA]
Great.
She's a stalker.
This chick is
seriously disturbed.
Now.
What did you do this for again?
[SENA]
Wait, I forgot to show you this!
Right.
Is that the same one Yozora had?
I might've kinda
bought it from her.
Perseverance for
vengeance, right?
Oh.
You mean like from that old
story about the guy who kept
feeding his anger against
his father's killer until
he finally got revenge.
He slept on firewood and
ate weird stuff, didn't he?
Yep.
There you have it.
By staring at Yozora's stupid
face every night when I go
to sleep while inhaling the
scent of the wig she wore.
I remember the humiliation
she's put me through and psych
myself up about making her
pay for her crimes one day.
I swear I'll make that
jerk beg me for mercy!
[KODAKA]
Sena Kashiwazaki.
The reason we need the
hot versus crazy scale.
Hey.
What?
Oh, right, uh,
about this problem.
[SENA] I already solved
that one for you.
I know that.
But I still kinda need to
know how to solve it myself
if I want to pass the final.
What?
How can you not understand
something so easy?
Are you stupid or what?
Fine!
Never mind.
I'll just do it myself.
Good. But try to do it faster.
[KODAKA] For a smart girl,
she is one awful teacher.
[STELLA]
Excuse me.
I've brought refreshments
for the two of you.
It's been a while, Kodaka.
I trust all matters
are progressing well.
Um.
Well, yeah, I guess so.
I understand.
Please use this
if the need arises.
I hope you both
enjoy yourselves.
Kodaka.
What did Stella
just hand to you?
[KODAKA]
N-Nothing.
It's nothing.
That woman has
a way of freaking me out.
[SENA]
Come on; show it to me.
Stop!
No.
Let go of it!
Show it to me!
What are you looking at, perv?
I-- I'm not looking
at anything, weirdo.
Fine.
I'm sick of studying.
How about we
play a game instead?
That's not why I came over here.
Well, I guess it's no biggie
as long as it's
just a little break.
Found it!
Do you wanna play this one?
Sure.
But be warned; I play
that with my sister a lot.
[KODAKA] I didn't know
you were into this.
Well, I haven't
had it very long.
Kobato's like a super huge
fan of the anime, isn't she?
Oh. Oh yeah.
I went ahead and got all
the Blu-rays when I picked up
the game, but I haven't
watched them yet.
I was waiting for the
next time Kobato comes over.
[KOBATO] Thank all things holy
I didn't bring her with me.
[RAYSIS] Shatter the very
soul of my enemy!
Nine Lives Breaker!
[VIDEO GAME]
K.O! You win!
Ha!
Ten in a row for me!
Suck it Sucker!
Yeah.
Pretty awesome considering
you were a total n00b
in the beginning.
I can't help it that I'm
a genius at everything I do.
[KODAKA] I wish I could
deny it, but I can't.
Crap, when did it get so late?
And we didn't get any studying
done for finals at all.
Ugh.
Whatever; I've gotta go home.
[knock on door]
[STELLA]
Excuse me.
Forgive me for
another interruption,
but dinner is ready
to be served now.
You heard the lady.
You might as well
eat before you head home!
Yeah.
Great.
[KODAKA]
Thank you for the meal, sir.
I should probably get back, now.
[PEGASUS]
Nonsense.
What?
You will be staying
with us for the night.
I-- what?
You are staying here
for the night.
I... Right.
[KOBATO]
♪ Ah-ah. ♪
♪ So long ago beneath
that lovely sky. ♪
[KODAKA] Why do I always
get so thrown off
when I'm in this house?
[wet footsteps]
[KODAKA]
President?
I'm here to wash your back.
[KODAKA] No, uh, thanks a lot;
but I'm actually good.
[PEGASUS] Yes, of course
you're circumspect as usual.
Hayato would be tossing the soap
at me without missing a beat.
Don't worry;
we're all friends, here.
[KODAKA]
Yeah, how good of friends?
How's that feel?
Uh.
It's fine.
That's just fine, sir.
Y'know, it's rather funny.
This brings back memories of
the very first time your father
took me to a bathhouse with him.
By the way, Kodaka?
[KODAKA]
Um. Yeah?
Well, I'm curious.
Do you know whether or not
my daughter is perhaps
being bullied at school?
No, I'm pretty sure
nothing like that's happening.
I see.
The reason I'm asking is-- well,
the other day Sena came home
with fried squid and
yakisoba piled on her head.
It may be difficult
to believe, but it's true.
Wow.
I had no idea, sir.
She said.
"This is a super
high-class hairstyle worthy
of my greatness."
Angry, I scolded her, but
now that I've calmed down,
I've realized something.
The truth of the matter
is that there's no way
such a ridiculous
hairstyle could exist.
My daughter is a very
proud young woman.
I was worried she might
have said those absurd things
to hide the fact that she's--
she's being bullied.
Yep.
That makes sense.
Um, Mister President.
Have you been inside
Sena's room recently?
[PEGASUS] No, not since
she's entered high school.
She doesn't really like me
to go in there for some reason.
I imagine that's perfectly
natural for a girl her age.
[KODAKA] I hate to tell you
this, sir. But you're daughter's
actually turned into
a psychopathic stalker!
I probably shouldn't say that.
Uh.
For what it's worth, sir.
I don't think
she's being bullied.
Probably.
[PEGASUS]
I hope you're right.
[KODAKA]
I swear to you.
If I ever saw Sena get bullied,
I would step in and protect her.
So try not to worry, sir.
[PEGASUS]
You would?
Of course you would!
She's in your care, Kodaka!
I know she'll be
in good hands with you!
Yep.
Yeah!
[KODAKA]
In my care?
That seems like
a lot of pressure.
Oh, whatever.
At this point, I had yet
to realize that I was
getting increasingly involved
in a situation that was
way out of my control.
[SENA]
One day, Yozora.
Just you wait!
This anime's second
season is finally kicking off!
In Season Two, now that
I've cut my hair and quit
screwing around, I'll be able
to do cool stuff more worthy of
the main heroine!
I'll be trusted in my rightful
place as the leader of
the Neighbor's Club and
maybe get a real life, too!
I might even get closer with
Kodaka and have the best year
of my whole life!
This is gonna be so rad!
Next time: Homo Game Club!
Man, I love this season.