[gum chewing]
[RIKA] So what made you
think you could get away
with this little stunt, huh?
I thought if I picked a movie
that wasn't all sparkly
and mainstream, you guys would
be too dumb to figure it out.
Oh it's fine if
you don't get caught?
Looks like the only
dumb one here is you, missy!
[YUKIMURA]
That was stupid.
And so lame.
[YOZORA]
Okay fine.
I'm very sorry.
So what the crap are we
supposed to do about this?
[KODAKA]
About what?
We don't have a film anymore.
Unless you think there's
a way we can still
use the stolen script?
We're not making money off it
and Rika doubts
anyone would know.
You've got to be kidding me!
Don't you know who I think I am?
I can't be in
some knock-off movie!
We're trashing
Yozora's fake script.
If I'm going to star in a film,
it's has to be an original.
Yeah, but there's no time
to write a whole new script.
That's the problem.
I'm not suggesting
we write a new one.
[SENA]
Ta-da!
Uh.
I can't see it.
What I hold in my delicate,
silky, royal hand
is an original script.
I wrote it on the sly
in case Yozora predictably
let us all down.
Of course you did.
Oh wow!
What an awesome title, Sena!
All that and
she's a writer, too!
Sing your songs of
gratitude quickly, my minions.
We've got work to do.
How does it feel, Yozora?
Losing such a great job to me.
This is the closest
I've ever come to meeting
a real life criminal.
Hope you enjoyed your
five minutes of fame.
I'll gladly pick up
the remaining ten
and spend them wisely.
La la and down came the
script-writing vulture!
I can't believe you actually
thought you'd get away with it!
Loser-Face!
Hold still!
That's a perfect look
for what I'm trying to do.
I hope you can act.
[BOY 1]
Look it's a witch!
[BOY 2]
So cool!
No self-respecting witch
would dress like this!
Are you listening
to me, Meat Breath?
Hello?
So it's 'boys over the' what?
The slope.
That's correct.
Okay everyone, let's take
it from the fight scene!
[YOZORA]
Fine.
[YUKIMURA] ♪ And no matter
what they tell me, ♪
♪ there's no going back now. ♪
Now.
[YOZORA screaming]
No!
What is this power?
I'll get you!
[YUKIMURA]
Goodness.
You're pretty good
at this acting thing.
That's perfect!
Now!
This is where you jump her!
And cut!
Crossfade to next morning!
What's a crossfade?
Yozora!
This is where you self-destruct!
How am I supposed to do that?
Oh please!
I don't know any actresses
who can't blow themselves up!
Don't worry!
Rika will cover that
in post with some CG!
I'll do everything I can
to make sure our friendship...
[BOTH]
Outlasts planet Earth!
Now, let us give
thanks for the--
[YOZORA]
...mercy we have been given.
We give thanks
to the all-knowing,
all-powerful goddess Swena!
Yes, indeed.
She is but love inside me.
I said "She's butt-love."
[KODAKA] High school
friendships, singing,
magic, super powers.
Intergalactic samurai robot wars
on top of guy-guy love scenes.
How do you put all that in a
script and have it make sense?
Oh well.
Whatever.
I guess we can always say
we're making an indie film.
[RIKA] Rika's very sorry for
bothering you like this.
She knows you're busy.
Hey, don't sweat it.
[KODAKA]
I just realized,
maybe I shouldn't be
walking alone with Rika.
You know.
Rika just realized we're walking
alone together down the hallway.
It's sort of
a first step, isn't it?
A first step for what?
I shouldn't have to tell you.
Hey, what was that noise for?
[RIKA]
And here we are!
Welcome!
I haven't been in this
room since we first met.
It still smells the same.
I don't even remember
how long ago that was.
[RIKA] It was one hundred
and twenty-two days,
eight hours and
thirty-seven minutes ago.
[KODAKA] Have you been
counting this whole time?
[RIKA]
No counting!
Rika just remembers!
Now if we broke it down by
seconds, that would require
actual counting and Rika
does not have time for that.
[KODAKA]
Sect Sigma?
[RIKA]
Tell no one if you want to live.
Whoa.
Rika used to have a fingerprint
and voice recognition code
on the lock to make it even
more like a secret hideaway.
That's intense, Rika.
You're more into this
nerdy stuff than I thought.
Do you also cosplay
while you're in here?
Rika can tell when someone
is making fun of her joy.
[KODAKA]
Whoa.
This is unbelievable.
You can go ahead
and set that equipment bag
down anywhere you like.
Cool.
This is crazy!
You're the first person Rika has
ever even let into this room!
Huh.
She pours her heart out
and all you've got for
Rika is a lousy 'huh?'
Aren't you moved?
A girl is inviting you
into her room alone for
the first time ever!
Just because you live in it
doesn't mean this place
qualifies as a 'girls room.'
All right, well I hope
all the equipment works out.
Let me know how it goes.
[RIKA]
Oh! Wait; don't go!
Rika wants your thoughts on
the special effects she added
to the scenes we shot yesterday.
[YUKIMURA] ♪ And no matter
what they tell me. ♪
♪ There's no going back now. ♪
Now.
What is this power?
I'll get you!
You're more powerful
than I thought you were.
Woah! You've done
an awesome job!
Aww!
Rika couldn't wait to show you!
She's glad you like it!
I love it.
It looks like an entirely
different movie!
How long did it take you?
A long time, but the
result was worth it!
Yeah, totally.
I feel bad you're doing
so much on your own.
Do you need help?
[RIKA]
Not at all!
It does take a while but Rika's
not stressed out about it.
Rika has worked on
fan-fic movies and some games
before but only by herself.
There's a little pressure this
time since she's doing this
for people she knows.
Especially since one of
those people is you.
Okay.
[KODAKA] What's the
Neighbors Club binder?
Oh.
Here, Rika will show you.
Don't freak out but Rika
took some secret photos.
[KODAKA]
I was changing, you perv!
Yes, but it isn't
what you think!
[KODAKA]
Then please start explaining.
[RIKA]
Rika needed them for reference!
Remember that time
we all played the
Romancing SaGa game together?
[KODAKA]
Yeah.
Rika wanted to make everyone's
CG players as accurate
as possible so she
used actual photos.
[KODAKA]
No way.
All that work just to create
a video game character?
I'm impressed.
[RIKA]
There you go.
Now you know everything.
Promise Rika you
won't judge her, okay?
I won't, but--
But what?
You hate it don't you?
Huh?
No.
I was just thinking
I should go.
Talk to you later.
[RIKA]
Oh.
Okay, yeah.
See you tomorrow.
[RIKA]
That's too bad.
Rika had a really great time.
It was the first time Rika ever
played a game with other people.
That's the most fun
she's ever had.
[KODAKA] She always has the best
attitude no matter what.
Out of all the Neighbor's
Club members, it seems
like making friends is
most important to her.
At least, she seems
to be trying the hardest.
[ATTENDANT]
Kids, this way!
Parents, wait there!
Here, take one.
Tell all your friends about us.
Wow!
That's a big bear!
Hey Big Brother, is it
okay if we get crepes?
[KODAKA]
Uh, sure.
But maybe later.
[MARIA]
Yay!
Best day ever!
Thanks for bringing me!
You're acting like you've
never been to a festival before.
I had no idea these kind
of things even happened.
Back when I was going
to school all we ever did
was work and study!
[KODAKA]
Right.
Uh, where's second year,
class two?
Ah, here we go!
They're in the A-V room.
Says they're
starting at ten A.M.
And of course we only have
five minutes to find it!
We need to hurry.
Where's the AV room?
I'm supposed to know this, how?
Maybe because you went
to this school two years ago?
Huh?
Sorry to disappoint you,
but that wasn't me.
Are you sure about that?
[SENA]
Yep.
I went to a public school
a few blocks away from me.
That's right.
I remember now.
You had to take the
entrance exam, didn't you?
There's no way you
were grandfathered in.
Thanks for the
biography, Yozora.
Let's go!
The AV room isn't going
to come looking for us!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Please take your seats.
Class Two, Second Year will
now present an original film.
We ask that you remain
silent during the screening
and turn off or
silence all cell phones.
Lucky for us.
They're running behind.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Thank you for your cooperation.
Class Two hopes you enjoy their
short starring Lady Kobato!
It's Lady Kobato now?
♪
[KODAKA]
She used her real name?
[KODAKA] It's like a reverse
Cinderella with dragons.
[KODAKA] Our movie just
got its butt kicked.
Brava, Kobato!
Two huge thumbs up!
[YUKIMURA]
That was beautiful.
Talent runs in the family.
You must be so proud of her.
Rika's more of an
action-adventure type,
but she can hang with a good
romantic drama now and then.
Me too.
It actually gave me ideas
for things we could do
with our mov-what now, Sena?
I can't get over
how cute she is!
She's like a teeny tiny doll
that you can
squish in your arms!
Kobato is the greatest actress
I've ever seen in my life.
And she's so hot!
Oh I know.
The entire audience was like,
melting in her hands.
And can we talk about
how our first showing
was almost overflowing?
If people keep
talking about it,
we're not gonna
have enough seats!
We should totally sell tickets.
People would buy them
just to see Kobato!
There she is, our
precious little starlet!
It's been such a long time since
I've seen you or smelled you!
I've missed you
bunches and bunches,
my little angel mouse-let!
You're so cute!
I need a princess whiff!
And you smell so amazing!
Get off me!
I can't breathe!
What are you guys
even doing here?
Kodaka you jerk!
I told you not to come!
[CLASSMATE]
Um, hi.
Are you Kobato's brother?
I've heard so much about you!
Oh.
Yeah.
What did you think?
Wasn't Kobato just unbelievable?
Yeah.
Everybody was.
In fact, the whole
movie was amazing!
Hey Kobato!
Your hottie big brother
thought you were amazing!
[SENA]
I totally agree, Kobato.
You blew my mind.
I thought you were
the best thing about it!
Sorry.
It looks like our diva
just needed a moment.
[CLASSMATE]
No worries.
So, uh is Kobato
popular here or something?
I'm a little
freaked out right now.
Yeah!
Duh!
And it's more than
just our class!
The whole school worships her
and wants to be her friend!
I had no idea!
[CLASSMATE]
Except.
Well, I don't know if that
actually makes her popular
since she doesn't
want to talk to anybody.
I kinda don't think
she likes people very much.
Okay, I shouldn't say
'people,' I guess just not us.
Very interesting.
[CLASSMATE] We're always telling
her how much we adore her,
but it's like the more we
try to get close to her,
the more she pulls away.
Or maybe she just
doesn't take us seriously.
Omigosh!
Please don't hate my guts!
I'm not trying to
badmouth your sister!
I love her!
I'm really a fan
of her awkwardness.
It's like, totes endearing!
See ya later!
Doesn't take compliments.
Pulls away when
you try to get close.
Sure sounds like that
runs in the family.
Huh?
Sorry, what did you say?
[KODAKA]
What's wrong, Maria?
I'm bored.
I wanna go home
and stuff my face.
Dry your mortal eyes.
You shall wait for me no longer!
The smelly vampire has
returned and we can kill her
once and for all!
Do we stone her?
Drown her?
How are we gonna do it?
Your idiocy amuses me
to no end, Minion of God.
Someday you will regret your--
Why do you keep
jumping out at me like that?
Are you trying
to get me to destroy you?
[MARIA] I can smell the
crazy leaking out of you!
[KOBATO] I have powers that
would have your God on His knees
begging me for lessons!
[MARIA]
So, get him some kneepads!
Okay let's get moving!
We can film Kobato's scene next
since she's already warmed up.
I didn't even know
Kobato was in this.
Yeah, of course she is.
I realize this might make it a
little awkward for you because
we've decided to have
her do all your scenes.
Is she replacing me or was I
just a stand-in
for her all along?
Look at that sunset!
It's the perfect locashe
for our next shot!
Let's go!
[YOZORA]
We're on it.
You can count on us.
It's no use,
you tragic excuse for a nun.
I'll crush you
with the same powers
that bewitched my audience!
Poopy vampire!
You think your
performance was so great?
You're in for a surprise!
[SENA]
Kobato wait!
You can play when we're done!
[SENA]
Kodaka! Let's move!
We're burning daylight!
Okay, okay, I'm coming.
[SPEAKER]
Good afternoon!
Look what the sunshine drug in!
Great day for a sports
festival, don't you think?
You've all worked so hard.
I hope you're as proud
of yourselves as I am of
the entire student body.
I'm excited to see the results
of all your efforts and talents.
[KODAKA] Nice, so our student
body president is a girl.
She's kinda hot.
What now?
I don't have anything to do
until they're ready for me.
[KODAKA]
Hey.
Are you bored, too?
Yeah, I'm probably just
going to head home soon.
[KODAKA]
Whoa!
What?
Why?
It's not a big deal.
I should've just skipped.
It's early and someone
already pissed me off.
Who would that be?
That skinny ponytail who
spoke at the opening ceremony.
No way!
I had no idea you even knew
the student body president.
Well, we've never actually
spoken, but I know enough
to know that I hate her.
Hinata Hidaka.
She's a third year, and
this is her second term as
student body president
so that should tell you
how ridiculously popular she is.
She's smart and good
at every sport imaginable.
All the teams ask her
to fill in for them.
Even though she's busy,
she will make time for
anyone who asks for a favor.
Of course all the freshmen think
she's like some kind of goddess.
[KODAKA] Yeah, why would anyone
like someone like her?
Well it's not just that.
It's because she's
so not fake about it.
I mean, Meat-McNasty does
all those sorts of things,
but she does it to get
people to worship her.
She doesn't actually
like anyone, ya know?
But Hinata--She's kinda
like King Lear in a way.
And what does that mean?
[YOZORA]
It's a Shakespeare play, idiot.
It's one of his most famous
tragedies about an old evil king
who causes his country nothing
but misery until his own
horrific death.
Pretty much the entire cast
dies in his wake.
Uh, that's kind of
a creepy comparison.
I think it accurately represents
my desire to see her suffer
the same amount of
pain she's caused me.
She's making me want
to puke just talking about her.
I need to go to the
nurse's office and lie down.
So you're allergic to
genuinely nice people.
Got it.
[KODAKA]
Rika?
What the hell is
she doing up there?
[RIKA]
Kodaka?
The hell are you doing here?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
Oh, um.
Rika likes the feel of the wind.
Well, you'll certainly get
a lot of it dressed like that.
Rika was feeling
sporty today so she decided
to wear her gym outfit.
What do you think?
Yep, that's the right one.
Why don't you go down
and participate?
Nah.
Rika's got a lot
of work left to do.
Not that she would
join in if she didn't.
Holy crap.
You stayed up all night working
on the movie, didn't you?
Oh gross.
Is it that obvious?
Rika was totally going to wear
her glasses today
but then she forgot.
Something tells me
I still would have known.
Anyway, I hope you
realize we appreciate you.
[RIKA]
Stop!
Stop giving Rika genuine
heartfelt compliments
without notice!
Her mind can't take it
and she's about to explode!
[KODAKA]
Sorry.
I take it back.
[RIKA]
Oh yay!
The race is about to start!
Here they go!
[gun shot]
[RIKA]
Look!
Sena's already got a head start!
Crapper duck, how does
she run with those things?
I don't know but you seem
pretty mad about it.
No, Rika's just impressed with
everything she can do on top
of looking that way!
[KODAKA]
Yep, she has a gift.
What are your thoughts?
Go ahead, Rika wants to know
all the dirty details.
There are no dirty details!
She's just another
club member, silly.
[RIKA]
She's also your betrothed.
That's crazy and it's not
even happening anymore.
Rika thinks that you might
want to update Sena
on that situation.
Huh?
Wait, what do you mean?
Rika doesn't understand how you
can complain that you're lonely
when you don't let
anyone get close to you.
You pretend not to
notice when someone
is interested in your life,
then you make jokes so that
no one will know
when you're upset.
Even though no one's given good
reason, you convince yourself
no one likes you
so you never get hurt.
[KODAKA, nervously]
I get it.
Is this what you
want to tell Kobato?
If so, go for it.
It sounds good!
That's not gonna work.
Rika knows that you
know the truth, but--
She will continue to play
the role you want her to play
and protect your secrets
so you're comfortable,
but for how long, Kodaka?
Rika predicts these games will
get old after a little while.
What about--
Shut up, Rika!
I gotta go.
Talk to you later.
Kodaka.
Please always remember.
Rika would bend over backwards
for you anytime, anywhere.
Huh?
Sorry, I missed a lot of that.
[KODAKA] She would bend over
backwards to help me
any time I needed it.
The wind may have swallowed her
words, but I've known the truth
about how Rika feels
for a very long time.
♪ You played dumb but my heart
knew the truth all along! ♪
♪ What? ♪
♪ You denied when Rika cried but
she saw right through you yeah ♪
♪ What? ♪
You're not exactly singing the
same song as Rika, are you?
I'm sorry.
I'll stop and try to collaborate
and listen this time.
What?
Next time!
Dismay of I, the Chicken.
Kodaka, will you marry Rika?
No love games.
Turn our bad romance around!
Um, no.
Not even for the song?