[PHONE]
You've got mail!
[KODAKA]
Sena?
What's this about?
[SENA]
Kobato's Happy Birthmas party!
I'm heading into town on
Sunday to shop for presents!
Do you think you can make it?
[KODAKA]
This coming Sunday?
Yeah, I think I'm free.
"Sounds good.
Let's meet up around one
o'clock at the train station.
See you there."
[PHONE]
You've got mail!
[RIKA moaning]
You ready for some fun?
Tie Rika to a telephone pole
and she'll take
whatever you give her!
Rika likes to be on top, but
she can't resist a forceful man,
the kind that goes
in on the first date!
Please call back,
Rika's ready and waiting!
[KODAKA]
"Leave.
Me.
Alone."
[RIKA]
Read it vertically!
[KODAKA]
Vertically, huh?
Rika wants you to take her
on a date, please.
No can do.
[RIKA]
Pretty please?
Rika needs your help in
picking a present for Kobato!
Then why didn't you
tell me that the first time?
[PHONE]
You've got mail!
[YUKIMURA] For the esteemed
Mister Kodaka Hasegawa.
Dear Mister Kodaka Hasegawa, I
hope this pleasant fall season
has brought you great wealth
and prosperity, particularly in
the forging of new friendships.
Please forgive me for the
suddenness of this letter.
I know its
arrival is unexpected.
I'm terribly sorry
to trouble you when you
are surely very busy, but I take
pen in hand now because there is
something of utmost importance
that I must ask you.
There is no other
companion I may consult.
I know you are a busy man,
so I shall be so bold as to
come straight to the point.
Your sister's birthday
is fast approaching.
What should I give
to your honored sibling?
With my best wishes
for your health--
I don't have time for a novel!
[PHONE]
You've got mail!
[YOZORA] Need your help
getting a present for Kobato.
No big deal if
you're busy or whatever.
I know how forgetful and...
[KODAKA]
Not you, too.
[YOZORA] Tomorrow would work
best, but whatever, it's not
like you absolutely have to
be there, so don't worry...
[KODAKA]
And it's super long.
What's with all the whatevers?
Oh well.
Hey.
Sup?
[MALE ANNOUNCER] The next
train is now approaching...
[KODAKA]
Looks like everyone's here.
Cool.
Guess we better get to it.
[KODAKA] Grab a seat,
Yozora, there's one right here.
[YOZORA] Shut up, don't
tell me what to do!
What's the rest of
the club doing here?
[KODAKA]
Oh, my bad.
Yeah, I guess I didn't tell you.
Everyone wanted to
buy Kobato a present,
so I figured we might as well
hit up the mall together.
Still.
This probably wasn't the best
way for you to go about it.
I mean it's not a secret
that you're pretty dense,
but this is beyond stupidity!
Did I do something wrong?
[SENA]
Never mind.
Idiot!
Rika had a feeling Kodaka was
going to let her down again.
But even though you know
it's coming, it still sucks.
I, too, feel your pain,
I think we all do.
All her studies couldn't have
prepared Rika for such a man.
Someone so-- so ridiculously
oblivious to everything.
Okay.
Oh, but it's really
not a big deal!
One day you'll feel
Rika's presence,
emotionally and physically!
I don't think I will.
By the way, why are you
wearing your lab coat today?
Why, is there a problem with it?
[KODAKA] You've been obsessed
with your hair lately
but you don't care
about your clothes.
It's kind of a
strange combination.
Like today, how you're
wearing the same clothes
but also randomly
got highlights.
Um.
Rika didn't think
you would notice.
Aren't you just
full of surprises!
But to be honest, Rika has never
thought that worrying about
her clothes would
make a difference.
There's no incentive,
considering you don't even
pay attention to her
when she's stripping.
[KODAKA]
Not gonna lie.
I wouldn't mind if she
ditched the lab coat and
wore something more revealing.
I take it I somehow said
all of that out loud again?
Yeah you did!
Let's go in the
back and make babies!
Oh yeah.
I've got a question, Sena.
[SENA]
What is it?
[RIKA] Rika wanted to buy
some new clothes while
we're shopping. Are there any
nice stores you'd recommend?
Uh.
You want my
shopping advice, really?
Rika would love to
learn from the master!
You're such a
stylish and sexy gal!
[SENA]
Actually.
I honestly don't go shopping
that often, and when I do
it's at the fancy name-brand
places near my house,
so I don't know
what to tell you.
The only places close to your
house are a few mountains
and rice fields.
Is that true, Sena?
No, Miss Sena is fibbing.
You're right,
I'm sorry I lied to you.
Stella's the one who
picks out all of my clothes.
She styles my hair
and puts on my makeup, too.
What was that for?
It's not like
you know any better!
Femininity level of only five?
How pitiful.
Hey, neat, a scouter!
[SENA] While we're at it, where
do you buy your clothes, Yozora?
I get all my stuff online.
If I see a model with a
decent-looking outfit in
a fashion magazine
or on a website,
I'll buy the whole thing.
Rika's jealous; it's awesome
that you can look good
wearing outfits straight out
of a fashion mag!
And today you
look especially cute!
This is cute?
Shut up!
[RIKA]
Uh-uh!
It's very feminine, and
such an adorable sort of sexy!
[YOZORA]
Feminine?
Adorable?
Sexy?
Uh, crap.
[YOZORA]
Take it back!
This was in the "How to
Look Boyish" section,
there's no way
this can be sexy!
Girl, are you for real?
Yozora, listen to me.
When women rock
the "boyish" look,
it doesn't mean they're
dressing like a man would,
in fact it's usually
the other way around.
It's a way to draw out
your feminine charms
by being more androgynous.
Think shorts instead of skirts
and knits instead of wovens.
Seriously, you'd have to be
blind not to notice this stuff!
How often do you see dudes
strutting around in hot pants
and showing off
their belly buttons?
[YOZORA] But you're the
only guy whose wardrobe
I ever even noticed.
Oh, just forget it!
[YOZORA] I'm gonna do some other
shopping after I get her gift.
Kodaka, you can't come along!
[KODAKA]
That's cool.
Are you gonna be
okay by yourself?
[RIKA]
Rika will keep her company.
Yeah, all right.
Yukimura, do you mind tagging
along with Yozora and Rika
and keeping them in line?
We wouldn't want them to
freak out in the middle of
a public place,
do you know what I mean?
Yes sir.
I've got it under control.
I'll see you later.
Best of luck
shopping for Kobato!
Thanks!
Yeah, you too!
Well then.
That's that.
Why don't the two of us
start looking around?
[SENA]
Hey Kodaka.
What's something I could
buy for Kobato that'd
make her like me more?
I know she's into
Fullmetal Necromancer.
[KODAKA] Yeah, but she's pretty
much got all the merchandise
she could want already.
Oh, and please, don't
get her any expensive stuff.
[SENA] You're a more considerate
big brother than I thought.
What would you recommend, then?
[KODAKA]
I'm almost out of ideas.
How 'bout something you'd like?
[SENA]
Duh!
I totally want Kobato!
[KODAKA]
You can't have her!
Hey.
Over here.
I just thought of a gift
I know for sure she'd like.
[SENA]
What's that?
[KODAKA]
Meat.
I mean meat the food,
not meat as in you!
I knew that, don't rub it in.
[KODAKA]
Steak, bacon, wings, anything.
Get her some jerky
and she's yours for life.
Maybe so, but a meat snack's
kind of a messed-up birthday
present, don't cha think?
[KODAKA]
Good point.
Jerky?
What am I thinking?
Meh, remember that as a last
resort for the time being.
I'm sure we'll
find other good stuff.
[KODAKA]
Oh my gosh!
They have it!
They have what?
[KODAKA]
It's so beautiful.
[SENA] Seriously, since when
is the girl supposed to keep
the guy company when
they go shopping?
Normally it's
the other way around!
[KODAKA]
Sorry.
[SENA] And what the heck's so
special about frying pans,
anyway?
[KODAKA]
You've got to be kidding me!
D-fol pans aren't just
any 'ol frying pans!
Here, lemme try and
break it down for you.
[SENA]
Not necessary!
You are the
weirdest person I know.
It's almost kind of really sad.
[KODAKA] There's
nothing wrong with
liking high-quality cookware.
You've got a lot more issues
than just that one, dummy.
[KODAKA]
Shut up.
What do you think is
taking the girls so long?
[SENA] Girls always take a
long time to finish shopping.
At least they do
in dating games.
[KODAKA] You learned that
from a video game?
Hey Kodaka?
What do you think of the other
girls in the Neighbors Club?
Like, do you like them?
[KODAKA]
What do you mean?
[SENA] Man, why are you
so-- Ugh, never mind.
Do you ever even think about
dating and having a girlfriend?
[KODAKA] I guess I wouldn't say
I don't not want to date.
[SENA] Thanks for
clearing that up.
[KODAKA] Well, for
right now my main goal is
to make some friends.
Think about it, a boring
guy without any friends
isn't going to
impress many ladies.
Girls'll think
of him as a loser.
I don't think
that's necessarily true.
Man, how are you
so--Ugh, never mind.
[KODAKA] Hey, why do
you keep saying that?
Ah, random question.
Um, well-- What do you think
about the fact that Yozora
and I used to be friends?
You know, when we were kids.
[SENA] I was honestly surprised
when you first told us,
but then I thought things over.
I don't think
it's that big a deal.
In fact, it doesn't
matter at all.
[KODAKA]
You mean you don't care?
Well I mean,
it's in the past, right?
The present is
what's really important.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Still, I haven't quite figured
out what Yozora's intentions
are with you.
[KODAKA]
With what?
Never mind.
I doubt I'm gonna
lose to her, anyway.
That's all.
[SENA]
Hey, before I forget.
And this is important, so please
make sure you remember it.
Don't think of
yourself as boring.
Anybody I like
can't be that lame!
[RIKA] Do you have any opinions
on Rika's new outfit?
This is what the clerk
recommended Rika try on for you!
[KODAKA]
Oh?
Well, it's-- I'd say that
whenever you try to look good,
you pull it off nicely.
Rika will interpret
that messed-up comment
as a compliment.
[YUKIMURA]
Um, Kodaka?
Do you think I look okay?
Yozora bought something else,
so she let me have this.
[KODAKA]
Damn Yukimura, that's hot!
Uh, I mean-- it
looks nice on you.
I'm very glad you like it.
Thank you.
Last but not least.
What the hell is that?
[SENA]
What are you wearing?
I'm so confused.
Woman, you're a disaster
in black cotton.
Oh, be quiet, flapjacks.
I'm not in the greatest
of moods right now.
[KODAKA]
A tracksuit?
I found it marked down
at a sports store.
Don't you like it?
[YOZORA] Anyway, all these
crowds are making me
kinda groggy.
I'll just grab something
for Kobato near my place.
See ya later.
[RIKA]
Rika's gonna head home, too.
Thanks for the fun.
[KODAKA]
Sorry Sena.
My bags are getting heavy
and I'm tired of
lugging them around.
[SENA]
Not you, too!
[YUKIMURA]
I shall accompany you, Kodaka.
[SENA]
You have got to be kidding me.
You guys are so the
worst shoppers ever!
[SENA]
There!
It's perfect!
But no surprise there.
Then again, do you think
Kobato will even enjoy having
a birthday party
that looks this lame?
[KODAKA] Cut us some slack, no
one here actually knows what
a normal birthday
party looks like.
This'll have to work for now.
[YUKIMURA] Along those same
lines, what are people supposed
to do at a birthday party?
Do you know, Kodaka?
[KODAKA] Uh, well, probably
eat cake and open presents
most of the time.
Though that doesn't
sound like a lot of fun.
[RIKA]
Maybe everyone plays games.
It's a party, after all.
[YOZORA]
Fat chance that's gonna happen.
The only games we have are
your wonky computer games
and Meat's pervy dating sims.
[KODAKA]
Oh please.
There's no way she's not coming.
[RIKA] Rika almost has all
the bugs figured out!
Yeah, too bad there aren't any
board games in here, though.
[SENA] We'll just stop by the
closest toy store and get one.
How about Twister?
[YOZORA]
You really are a pervert.
[KODAKA]
If you're right outside
the door then you
should just get in here!
Happy birthday,
my sweet darling Kobato!
Likewise.
Happy birthday Miss Kobato.
Popper!
Enough with the poppers, guys.
[SENA]
Okay, Kobato!
Take a seat!
It's time for your cake!
Three, two, one, cake-off!
Dig in!
What do you think?
Isn't it beautiful?
We're so happy!
[YOZORA]
Wow, Meat.
Your creepiness
never ceases to amaze me.
What's your problem?
That cake is
incredible and you know it!
♪ It's a nice day
for a birthmas. ♪
[EVERYONE]
♪ Happy birthmas for you. ♪
♪ Who was born today? ♪
--It was honorable sister.
--It was Kodaka's little sister.
[KODAKA] Come on, at least
get her name in sync!
[EVERYONE]
♪ Happy birthmas to you! ♪
I hate that.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Blow out your candles!
Oh.
Um, okay then.
[EVERYONE]
Congratulations!
[KODAKA]
There you go!
[SENA]
What'd ya do that for, hobag?
[YOZORA]
Whoops.
My finger slipped.
[RIKA]
Open wide, Kodaka!
They're each a different scent!
[YUKIMURA]
It's a talisman.
Huh.
[KODAKA]
So, you got her meat.
Raw meat.
[SENA]
Don't mock me!
You're bound to eat some, too.
[YOZORA]
Meat giving meat.
How original.
I've got a good idea.
Let's have sukiyaki tonight!
Pretend that I'm right
there spoon-feeding you
my meat of love!
[KOBATO]
No!
[KOBATO giggling]
Sukiyaki!
[KODAKA]
Someone's in a good mood!
Today's been an awesome day!
[KODAKA] Hey, I've got to
pick up some ingredients.
Meet you back home
in a little bit, okay?
[KOBATO] Do your best not
to dawdle, my kinfolk.
Yo.
I didn't see you!
Why are you here?
[KODAKA]
Um, that's my house.
Why are you sneaking around?
Oh, I was just hoping I
could catch a glimpse of how
it looks inside.
That's all.
Silly, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Why do you even care
how my place looks?
Big Brother's finally home!
And another unexpected visit!
Did you get Kate to
bring you over here?
Yep!
If there's anything
the old hag is good for,
it's taking me to see you.
Wah!
What are you still doing here?
Stinkin' brat, weren't you
just begging and pleading,
"Please take me sis,
I'll be grateful forever!"
So what was that just now?
Care to explain yourself?
[MARIA]
Um.
I was-- Get lost, poopy old hag!
[KATE] Honestly, something's
wrong with that girl.
[KODAKA] Says the creepy chick
who's been spying.
Hey, since you two
are here already,
do you want to
stay over for dinner?
[KATE]
Seriously?
Both of us?
Uh, yeah.
[KOBATO]
Just perfect.
This wonderful day has now
turned into complete crap.
So you must be Big Brother's
one and only real
little sister, huh?
Who is your big brother?
Oh, that's what
Maria calls Kodaka!
She always wanted
a bigger brother.
So if I'm her sister, and
he's also older than me,
then he's my big brother, too.
Which totally makes you
and I sisters!
What's wrong?
Crappy stupidhead!
You big fat dummy!
How come you have so
many little sisters now?
I'm supposed to be
the only sister!
Quit making more!
[KODAKA]
Whoa, calm down!
They just call me Big Brother,
it doesn't mean anything.
Hey, why did Maria
want to come over today?
She said she wanted
to talk to Kobato.
What business does that foolish
minion of God have with me,
supreme ruler of
darkness and destruction?
[KATE]
What just happened?
Just pretend
you didn't see that.
Hey, come on Maria!
Hurry up and give Kobato the
present you bought for her!
--Maria brought a gift?
--Crapface brought a gift?
[MARIA]
Aaah!
Why'd you have to open
your big mouth, poopy old hag!
Why're you
freaking out about it?
[MARIA]
Here!
I decided to be nice
and get you a present,
so you better like it.
Birthdays are kind of important,
even for a poopy
vampire like you.
Just open it up and
say thanks already.
It's for scaring off evil
spirits and spooky stuff.
You should use it to drive
out the darkness from your
poopy soul and
become a good girl!
What a silly little
birthday present.
Divine powers don't work on me!
How dare you!
Repent your dumb sins,
you evil poopy vampire!
Your stupid key has no effect!
Does too, poopmeister!
All right ladies,
it's sukiyaki time.
Sukiyaki?
That's that tasty-sounding
meaty dish that the dumb hag's
too stupid to make!
Hold on Big Brother,
lemmie help you set the table!
Go on, Kobato.
Tell Maria thank you
for the birthday present.
Oh.
Thank um--Thank--
Thank you, ah, poop.
Did you just
say something to me?
[KOBATO]
Never mind, dumb-butt!
[MARIA]
What was that for, pooper?
[KOBATO]
Jerkface!
[MARIA]
Devil dummy toilethead!
Gimmie back that present!
Kneel and repent your poopiness!
[KATE]
Thanks for the awesome meal!
[KODAKA]
I barely got any beef!
There were at least
four pounds worth, too!
[KATE] Those girls have
quite the appetite!
[KODAKA]
Hey, so do you.
[KATE] All that food
is making me tired.
Hey Kodaka.
Do you mind if
we stay the night?
It's okay by me.
Seriously?
Thanks bro!
There is no way
you're only fifteen.
Fine, I turned
sixteen a while back.
Here, check this out.
Maria gave it
to me on my birthday.
Hey, that's a nice locket.
What's with the bug?
Maria gave me the cicada shell,
and I got a buddy to make it
into a totally wicked necklace.
It's the only thing that
girl has ever given me.
Your life has been
kind of rough, huh?
Hey, I'm a big sister;
it is what it is.
Maria!
Big Brother's letting us
stay for the night.
[KATE]
Come on, get up.
You need a bath.
[MARIA]
I want one with Big Brother.
[KATE]
Hurry it up, girl!
I decided to be nice and wash
you, so you better behave!
I'll check and see if we have
any pajamas that'll fit you.
[MARIA]
Let me go, poopy old hag!
[KATE]
Shut up and hold still!
I'm glad Kobato isn't
that hard to deal with.
[KODAKA]
Kobato?
[KATE]
You gonna take a picture?
No!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
[KATE] No wonder you
wanted us to stay the night.
I'm sorry about that, Kate.
[KATE]
Fine, I forgive you.
Well, that was quick.
Well, I'm pretty sure you
didn't stumble in on purpose.
[KODAKA]
Of course I didn't, geez!
Exactly, so it's not worth
getting all pissed off at you.
It's cool that you're
not making up excuses or
trying to defend yourself.
[KODAKA]
Yeah, when I do something bad,
I think it's best
to own up to it.
You really are
a halfway decent guy.
It totally makes sense
why Pegasus likes you
as much as he does.
[KODAKA] Oh, do you and the
president know each other?
Sure, me and Pegasus are
actually fishing buddies.
We go out ayu fishing
once or twice a month.
[KODAKA]
That's super random.
[KATE]
It's fun.
You oughta come along sometime!
Yeah?
Maybe someday.
[KATE] Hey, thanks for
letting us crash.
Till next time!
[KODAKA]
Yeah.
See you guys at school.
[KATE] Man, sometimes
I wish that you really were
our bigger brother.
Then again.
To be honest.
I wouldn't mind if you
were more than just a brother,
because that way you could
walk in on me all the time.
But you do have Sena,
so-- Well that's out.
Alrighty, see ya!
[KODAKA]
It wasn't long before
I figured out what Kate
was getting at.
It wasn't very long at all.
Ah, that was delicious!
Let's go home and take a nap.
Hey!
Do the preview like
a normal person, hag!
Yeah, whatever,
you annoying brat.
Next: "My Childhood Friend Is
Too Much of a Battleground."
If Big Brother has
childhood friends,
that means he's all grown up!
I wanna have a
childhood friend, too!
Don't be dense, you're
still in your childhood.
Though in another five years,
I bet Kobato could be
your childhood friend!
I don't want no poopy vampire
to be my childhood friend!
You and her will be
my enemies forever!
Take that, poopy hag!
Fine, fine!