[RIMURU]
The Jura Tempest Federation
and the Armed Nation of Dwargon
formed an official alliance.
And that's how the newly
established nation of monsters
managed to gain
powerful support.
I've returned once more, Rimuru.
Obviously, but why are you back?
[GAZEL] Ah, to bring you a gift,
of course.
What is it?
[GAZEL]
Hmm.
[RIMURU]
A body?!
Wait, isn't that Vesta?
[VESTA groaning]
It's wasteful to let
a gifted man like Vesta
sit around and do nothing.
You see, he hasn't been allowed
to work for me since the trial.
Give him a job.
But, my king,
you should think about
the needs of Dwargon.
The dwarves will surely suffer
without his knowledge.
Bold words from someone who left
Dwargon behind himself.
-[KAIJIN gasps]
-Our nations are allies now.
Sharing resources is what we do.
This is your chance to develop
your country even further.
Vesta.
Uh, yes?
I want you to study here.
Devote yourself to it.
I shall.
This time,
I promise.
I promise I'll live up
to your expectations, my king.
Lord Rimuru.
Kaijin.
I am truly sorry.
If you would allow it,
then it would be my honor
to work here and serve you.
Well, having another
talented researcher around
would be a big help.
Listen, Rimuru,
if anything should happen,
I'll take responsibility.
I'll supervise Vesta.
So, please, say yes.
Thank you, Kaijin.
If this is what you really want,
Kaijin, then I trust you.
Vesta, you're hired.
[VESTA]
Thank you.
And I promise I will
give you nothing
but my best efforts, sir.
Well, then, I take my leave.
[applause]
[sighs]
Okay, then.
Now, why are you here?
Uh... [laughing]
I, the illustrious Gabiru,
have traveled here
hoping I might
be able to assist you.
You're the greatest, Sir Gabiru.
It's true, you know.
I'll get rid of him.
Please just hear me out!
Okay, the real reason
we came here
is because we want to
join your ranks.
On my honor, I swear
that we'll prove to be
useful to you, so please.
[ALL]
Please, my lord.
Like he said,
we just wanna help you.
My brother knows he was wrong.
All he wants to do
is repay his debt.
Aren't you captain
of the guard?
Yes, and unlike my brother,
I was not cast into exile.
[GABIRU]
Hey!
Instead, my father sent me here
hoping that I'd learn
more about the world.
Wait, so you didn't come
because you missed me?
-Ew, no.
-[GABIRU screams]
Yeah, that makes sense.
[RIMURU] And that's how
Vesta, Gabiru, his sister
and their brethren
joined our nation.
[GABIRU] You've always been
kind of a brat.
[RIMURU]
Since they were now our allies,
I decided to give
Gabiru's sister
and her servants some names.
Okay, let's go with
Soka, Toka, Saika,
Nanso, and Hokuso.
Thank you for this honor.
-[GABIRU whines]
-[RIMURU gasps]
-Gabiru.
-[GABIRU] Huh?
Don't give me
those puppy dog eyes.
Don't be jealous, you've already
got a name, it's Gabiru.
[gasps]
What the...
[yelling]
[RIMURU]
Gabiru's shining?
Wait.
Can I override
someone else's name?
[GABIRU]
Wow, thank you so much!
I'll follow you
as long as I live!
[groans]
[RIMURU]
Naturally, after that,
I had to give names
to all of Gabiru's friends.
Which caused the lizardmen
to evolve into dragonewts.
So they want to join us?
And may I use them
however I wish?
[RIMURU]
Sure.
I'm trusting you
to train them, Souei.
Right, as you command,
Lord Rimuru.
Thank you, sir,
I promise we'll work hard.
[RIMURU] I left Soka
and the others in Souei's care,
and found some work
for Gabiru and his men.
Well, that's weird.
After they evolved,
some of the lizardmen
ended up looking almost human.
I sent Gabiru's crew
to cultivate
the valuable hipokute herbs
in Veldora's cave.
Since it's a damp place,
it ended up being
the perfect home for them.
[RIMURU]
'Sup, Gabiru?
How's the growin' goin'?
[laughs]
I'm so happy you asked.
It's going swimmingly.
Feast your eyes on the fruits
of my labor, Lord Rimuru.
[RIMURU]
Let's see.
[GABIRU screams]
[RIMURU]
That's just a weed!
What? Really?
Forgive me, my lord.
In my haste to produce results,
it seems I've only
disappointed you.
[RIMURU]
Come on, man.
If anything, weeds should be
harder to grow
in a place
dripping with magicules.
[RIMURU]
In the back of the cave,
we set up a place
where Vesta
could conduct his research.
Currently he's focusing
on creating new healing potions
from the hipokute herbs.
If we can somehow
mass-produce potions
that are as effective
as the ones that I make,
it would really give us
an advantage.
A lot has happened.
But it looks like we can finally
take things easy.
[inaudible]
[MILIM]
Interesting! Very interesting!
I'd like to go investigate
this new toy, personally.
Now, now, Milim.
Don't forget about our pact
with the Forest of Jura.
What? But it's so dumb.
I mean, with Veldora gone,
can't we just ditch
the whole non-aggression pact?
There's an idea.
I don't see why not.
Right, then it's decided.
But promise we won't interfere
with each other.
-Fair enough?
-Seems reasonable.
Well, okay.
As long as everyone's
in agreement.
I'm off to go play
with my new toy.
Make sure you stay outta my way,
Clayman, Carrion and Frey.
[RIMURU gasps]
I just sensed something.
It almost feels like
there's a magical meteor
barreling straight towards us.
[whooshing]
[indistinct chatter]
[explosion]
[grunting]
[MILIM]
Nice to meet you.
I'm the one and only dragonoid,
known as the Destroyer.
People call me
the Demon Lord Milim Nava.
[RIMURU]
She's a Demon Lord?
I heard that you're
the strongest monster
in the forest now.
So I came to say hello.
[RIMURU] Holy crap,
I think her power level
might actually be on par
with Veldora's.
She's definitely the real deal.
[RIMURU gasping]
Uh, nice to meet you, too.
I'm Rimuru,
the leader of this town.
It's pretty impressive
that you could tell
that a little slime like me
was the strongest one here.
[chuckles] Nah, when you're
as amazing as I am,
gauging someone's
strength is easy.
See, my draconic "Milim Eye"
can detect the level of
magicules in whoever it sees.
[RIMURU]
Oh. Sounds legit.
Right, so there's no point in
pretending to be a weak slime,
because I know better.
I wonder if that's similar
to my skill, "Appraisal."
Not that it matters,
I don't really need
that skill to see she's flat.
What should I do?
I'm pretty sure there's no way
I could win against her.
[MILIM]
Huh?
[RIMURU]
She's a Catastrophe level.
Hey, is this slime thingy
your true form?
In Gelmud's ball
you looked different.
You had this long silver hair.
And looked kinda human.
[inaudible]
[RIMURU] Sounds like you know
everything, then.
[RIMURU grunts]
Was this the person you saw?
[MILIM]
Ooh! Then, it was you.
That is so neat.
Does that mean you defeated
the Orc Lord?
It was a tough battle,
but, yeah, I won.
So, uh, do you have
business with me?
You didn't come here to like,
avenge Gelmud or anything,
did you?
Huh? I already told you.
I just wanted to say hello.
[RIMURU]
That's it?!
Huh?
Die!
-[RANGA] Come, master.
-[RIMURU gasps]
[yelling]
[RIMURU]
Hey!
[RANGA]
I'm sorry, master, we must flee.
-[MILIM laughs]
-[SHION gasps]
[MILIM]
What's this?
Are you here
because you wanna play?
-[RIMURU] Stop!
-[RANGA whines]
[chuckles]
[yells]
[SHION grunts]
[gasps]
You may be a Demon Lord,
but not even you should be able
to escape from these bindings.
Now you die!
♪
Hopefully we at least caused
a little bit of damage.
[MILIM laughs]
Wow, that was pretty impressive.
You know, that attack might have
actually worked
on a different Demon Lord.
There's no way
they would have escaped
that big blast
in one piece.
Still though,
your pitiful attacks
have no effect on me!
[BOTH groan]
[RANGA]
Master!
♪
[groaning]
[RIMURU]
Are you okay, Shion?
Here, it's a potion.
Lord Rimuru.
Run, my lord.
Save yourself.
We will buy you time.
Here, guys, catch.
Drink those and rest.
I'll handle this one.
Interesting.
So, playtime isn't over yet?
Fine by me.
I'd love to play with you
a little bit more.
Lord Rimuru.
Well, if I give up,
it's all over.
And I can't do that.
Not yet, anyway.
Really?
Does that mean
you're gonna face me?
You seem confident, but you
still haven't tasted my attacks.
[laughs]
Okay, then.
I do love a good challenge.
However, if for some reason
your attack doesn't work,
you have to swear that you'll
serve me as my subordinate.
It's a deal.
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
To the nearest,
measurable degree,
her magicules are ten times
higher than yours.
[RIMURU] She hasn't even
been taking this seriously,
and she's ten times
stronger than I am?
In that case,
there's only one attack
that'll work.
[MILIM chuckles]
♪
Eat this!
What magic is this?!
I've never tasted anything
so delicious
in my whole entire life!
[RIMURU]
Score.
-You know, Demon Lord Milim...
-[MILIM] Huh?
If you admitted
defeat to me right now,
I'd be willing to give you
the rest of this "magic."
[groaning]
[RIMURU] The "magic" is honey
I found in the forest.
I want it so badly!
But I can't just admit
defeat to him.
I am a Demon Lord, after all.
Wow, it's so tasty.
[MILIM gasps]
[RIMURU]
Darn it all to heck,
looks like I'm starting
to run out.
[MILIM]
Wait. Hold on a second.
I have an idea. A draw.
We can call it a draw,
just this once.
And I'll forget this whole
attack ever happened, okay?
Is that all?
No, don't be silly,
of course that's not all.
Uh, what if I gave you my word
that I would never attack
any of you ever again?
[RIMURU]
And checkmate.
Her power may be overwhelming,
but on the inside she has
the heart of a child.
Very well,
I accept your proposal.
And, sure, just this once,
we can call it a draw.
[gasping]
[RIMURU]
And that's how we managed to win
over a Catastrophe-level
Demon Lord.
♪
Mm!
This is amazing!
So yummy!
[RIMURU]
Glad you like it.
I wish she'd take
her honey to go,
I really don't want
any more problems.
[MILIM]
Oh, hey.
Have you ever thought about
maybe becoming
a Demon Lord yourself?
[RIMURU]
Nah, it honestly sounds like
it'd be a pain in the slime.
Huh? Come on, seriously?
But we're great.
Doesn't everyone
wanna be like us?
[RIMURU]
Ah, hell no.
[BOTH gasp]
[RIMURU]
Does something cool happen
when you become a Demon Lord?
[MILIM]
Yeah, strong opponents
come and challenge you to fight.
It's fun.
[RIMURU]
They do that enough already.
-Count me out.
-What?!
So then what kind of things
do you do?
[RIMURU]
Lots of stuff.
My days are like crazy busy.
Do Demon Lords do anything
besides fight other people?
No, not really.
But we get to boss
Majin around all day.
[RIMURU] Uh, doesn't that
just mean you're bored?
[MILIM gasps]
[RIMURU]
Yep, her face says it all.
Well, I should get back.
Safe travels and all that.
Hold on.
You're doing something
way more fun
than being a Demon Lord,
aren't you?
-[RIMURU] No.
-No fair!
I wanna play, too!
Let me...
[RIMURU]
But I'm not playing!
Whatever it is you're doing
all day, I wanna do it, too!
In fact, I wanna go see
your village right now!
[RIMURU]
That's enough!
Okay, fine.
But on one condition.
You must always refer to me
as Mister Rimuru.
Screw that. I'm stronger.
You should respect me
and call me Lady Milim.
[RIMURU]
Let's compromise.
I'll call you Milim,
and in turn,
you can call me Rimuru.
How's that?
Okay, but only you, nobody else.
Normally I would only allow
another Demon Lord
to address me
in such a causal manner.
[RIMURU]
Awesome, thanks a bunch.
So, I guess that means
you and I are friends?
Uh, right.
[RIMURU]
I'll show you my village,
but you have to promise me
you won't cause any trouble.
You got that, Milim?
Don't worry about me, I promise
to be on my best behavior.
[BENIMARU]
That's Lord Rimuru for you.
He made taming Demon Lord Milim
look easy.
[RANGA]
Indeed.
[SHION]
I never doubted him.
[SOUEI]
I shall go tell Rigurd
about our new visitor
right away.
[MILIM laughing]
-[GABIRU] Oh?
-[MILIM] Huh?
[GABIRU]
Who might this be?
Hi there, little runt.
-[MILIM grunts]
-[GABIRU screaming]
[gulps]
[groaning]
Do you have a death wish?
Call me a runt again.
[RIMURU]
This is her best behavior?
Listen.
I promised Rimuru
that I would behave.
So I only used
a bit of my power.
But next time
I won't be so generous.
[GABIRU screams]
Look, there's Father,
he's waving at me
from across the river
to the Great Beyond.
[RIMURU] Your father's
still alive, you dork.
[GABIRU]
Huh?
By the way,
who is this little--
[MILIM growls]
[GABIRU]
Uh, grown-up-looking lady?
[RIMURU]
This is Milim.
Word is that she's a Demon Lord.
Whoa, seriously?!
[RIMURU]
I get it, but be chill, dude.
Listen, Milim,
you can't go slugging the crap
outta people when you get mad.
[MILIM]
Hmm.
Well, then, he shouldn't
have insulted me.
It's not my fault
he can't handle how I say hello.
[RIMURU] Nobody can handle
how you say hello.
So, don't do it.
[whimpers]
[RIMURU] Allow me to introduce
our new ally.
She's visiting here
as a special guest,
so please treat her
with respect.
Hi, I'm Milim Nava.
No way.
Milim as in the Demon Lord?
I never thought there'd
come a day
where I'd get
to meet her in person.
You're the greatest,
Lord Rimuru!
Wow, to think he befriended
such a tyrant.
Thanks to his efforts,
Tempest might be able
to exist in peace now.
[RIMURU]
Who knew Milim was so famous?
Everyone's excited
that she's here.
I'll be living here
starting today.
-Thank you.
-[RIMURU] What?!
[CROWD cheering]
You mean like live "here"
live here?
Yeah, what else would I mean?
I'm excited to live
in your monster town.
[RIMURU]
Uh...
Well, right, what she said.
Starting today, we have
a brand-new resident.
[CROWD cheering]
[RIMURU]
She sure is popular.
[MILIM] And if you need anything
at all, I'm happy to help.
[RIMURU]
I can't believe we're friends.
Yeah, I know.
It doesn't feel quite right.
[RIMURU]
Oh, you could hear me?
And I think...
we aren't actually friends.
-We are best friends!
-[CROWD cheering]
[RIMURU]
Best friends? Ah!
We are, right?
[MILIM whimpering]
[RIMURU]
We're definitely besties!
Hey, everyone,
we're besties for resties!
[CROWD cheering]
[CROWD chanting]
Besties for resties!
Besties for resties...
Meanie.
You really had me going there
for a second, Rimuru.
[RIMURU] And that's how
the Demon Lord, Milim,
a powder keg disguised
as a little girl,
came to live in
the Jura Tempest Federation.
[sighs]
What is this place?
It's so warm and relaxing.
[RIMURU]
One of the dwarf brothers, Myrd,
made it for me.
It's a bath that utilizes
the local hot springs.
Wow, it's so big!
You can even swim.
[SHION chuckles softly]
You shouldn't be swimming
in the bath.
[SHION gasps]
You either.
[SHION sighs]
[RIMURU]
Okay, then.
I think I've cooked enough,
I'm ready to get out
for the night.
I wish we could make
coffee milk.
The milk part is easy enough,
but the coffee part...
Then again, we've managed
to plant other things.
-[RIGURD] Lord Rimuru.
-[RIMURU] Huh?
[RIMURU]
What's up, my guy?
It's about Lady Milim.
I never imagined a Demon Lord
would take the initiative
to come here.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, but it should be fine,
after all she did promise not
to cause trouble or anything.
While true,
there is some concern
about whether or not
the other Demon Lords
have noticed us.
[ALL]
Hmm.
[RIMURU]
What do you mean?
Naturally, there are
several Demon Lords.
And they usually keep
a close eye on each other.
You see, by bringing Lady Milim
to our village,
and then declaring that you have
a close friendship with her,
it places our town
under her protection.
Under normal circumstances,
that would probably
be a good thing, but...
What he's trying to say,
Lord Rimuru,
is that you're the leader
of this village.
You have to realize that when
the other Demon Lords find out
that you've personally
befriended Lady Milim,
it will appear to them as though
the Great Forest of Jura
has entered into
an alliance with her.
Which also means that Lady Milim
would gain more influence.
Upsetting the balance
between the Demon Lords.
[RIMURU]
Oh, I see.
Still though,
what choice did we have?
It's not like we could
have refused
a Demon Lord of her power.
Yes, her abilities
are on a different level.
Thanks to Lord Rimuru,
Souei and I
are still sitting here.
Exactly.
And if the other Demon Lords
were to become hostile,
I doubt that we'd fare
any better against them.
But thankfully,
we can just leave everything
up to Lord Rimuru
seeing as he and Lady Milim
are besties for resties.
[ALL]
That's true.
[RIMURU]
You jerks!
Lady Milim is one of the most
powerful Demon Lords
of all of them.
And as far as Demon Lords go,
she's one you want to avoid
making an enemy out of.
So we have no choice
but to leave everything in your
capable "hands," Lord Rimuru.
[HAKUROU laughs]
[RIMURU] In the end,
I just rolled with it,
but I had no idea
that the whirlwind
Milim had managed to stir up,
was only just beginning
to gain traction.
[chuckling]
Splash battle!
Hyah!
Please stop, Lady Milim,
I thought I told you
not to play.
[SHION grunting]
Fine!
[MILIM]
Oh, it's on!
-Prepare for war!
-[SHUNA] I said no playing!
[MILIM chuckling]
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time, "The Gathering."