[crickets chirping]
[WOMAN]
I'll make you pay.
You will pay!
Curse that demon!
I swear you'll regret this.
Come on!
Come to me!
[gasps excitedly]
[DEMON laughs]
Who dares to summon me
from such a lowly station?
Is it you?
Yes, I called you here
to grant my request.
I don't care if you're a demon.
You can have my soul
if you want.
Just please, I'm begging you.
Kill them!
[chuckles]
Very well.
I suppose granting your wish
will at least
relieve me of my boredom.
[groans]
Thank you, sir.
And for my payment...
Mm-mm!
Nice.
That does complete our contract.
Your emotions were
absolutely tantalizing.
And for that, I shall do you
a great service.
That said,
I fear your payment
will only cover
about three days, at the most.
For an extension, well,
I suppose I can always
help myself to your prey.
[laughing]
I've been away from
the living world for too long.
I shall enjoy my time here
to the fullest.
[RIMURU]
The Kingdom of Filtwood.
A nation that borders
the Great Forest of Jura.
Shizu traveled there in response
to an urgent request.
The request was to defeat
a demon who had been revived.
[KNIGHT] Hello and welcome
to Filtwood Castle.
I can't tell you
what an honor it is
to meet the famous
Conqueror of Flames in person.
Follow me inside.
This way, please.
I'll show you
the reception hall.
[ALL gasp]
[ADVENTURER 1]
Shizue Izawa!
[ADVENTURER 2]
The Conqueror of Flames.
[ADVENTURER 3]
I'm so glad she's here.
[SHIZU]
Wow.
They've managed to gather
quite a few adventurers.
Hey. Long time no see.
[SHIZU]
It's been a while, Cougar.
Guess this means
you answered the request.
[SHIZU]
It's not as if I could refuse.
[COUGAR chuckles] Come on,
you're always so serious, Shizu.
I'm sure if you wanted you could
have found a reason to ditch it.
[SHIZU] And yet, here you are,
talking to me.
[COUGAR] Whatever. We both know
I'm only here for the money.
Although, I'm already
starting to regret it.
Supposedly, there have been
ten adventurers
who've already died.
[SHIZU]
How unfortunate.
But, hey, now that we've got
a champion on our side,
there's nothing to worry about.
[SHIZU]
I wouldn't go that far.
-[metallic clang]
-Huh?
[ADVENTURERS murmuring]
[COUGAR]
It's the minister.
Thank you all for coming.
I have some unsettling news.
We have just received word
that our champions,
the two Silver Wings,
have passed away.
-[ADVENTURER 1] What?
-[ADVENTURER 2] Impossible.
[ADVENTURER 3]
Are you serious?
[MINISTER] It appears
that their bodies were devoured,
leaving behind
only their clothes.
The request given to you is to
defeat the resurrected demon.
A similar account was found
in a century-old text.
The champion, Orthos.
[MINISTER]
Unfortunately, all we were able
to learn from this passage
is that the demon
was successfully sealed away
by the knight, Orthos.
And it does not mention
how he sealed it.
We have no choice
but to rely on you
if we hope
to defeat this demon.
[ADVENTURER 1]
That's not enough information.
[ADVENTURER 2] We're not
throwin' our lives away.
Listen, the Silver Wings
were heroes strong enough
to have titles.
If they failed,
there aren't enough lives
between us to survive this mess.
[SHIZU]
He's right.
Sorry, but this
is too dangerous.
You can count me out.
Please wait.
We're going to need help
from every person in this room
if we're going to
defeat this demon.
I don't care.
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
[murmuring]
Not good.
[MAN squeals]
Let's try to keep a cool head.
Besides, we do have
some good news,
and it's that we happen to know
what the demon is after.
And what's that?
There are remains that have been
laid to rest here,
in the castle's underground
reception hall.
Those remains are not human,
but the demon's body.
We believe his objective is to
recover what's left of his body
and complete his resurrection.
-Its remains?
-But why?
[murmuring]
Huh?
Ah! Is that
the famous Shizue Izawa I see?
I will gladly answer
your questions.
[SHIZU]
If it's true that the demon
nearly drove this kingdom
to the brink of ruin
and defeated
the two Silver Wings,
it's possible that we might be
dealing with an Archdemon.
[MINISTER]
Uh...
[SHIZU]
Which brings me to my question.
[MINISTER]
Huh?
[SHIZU] I was wondering
if this demon has a name.
[ADVENTURERS murmuring]
[RIMURU] When a monster
is granted a name,
it becomes more powerful.
Any capable adventurer
knows this fact
and would choose
their next move accordingly.
No, there are no accounts
indicating that the demon
had a name.
[ALL gasp]
[SHIZU]
If he doesn't have a name,
then he can't be an Archdemon.
Still, it's hard to imagine
the Silver Wings
losing otherwise.
So what is your intention?
Gather all
the adventurers together
and then wait
for the demon to arrive?
[MINSTER]
Yes.
With the Silver Wings now gone,
this strategy is our only hope
of defeating the creature.
[SHIZU]
Except at the moment
we're being treated
more like enemies
than potential allies.
Well, screw that!
You guys can't force us
to serve this stupid country.
See ya.
[MAN groans]
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
He's killed him.
[ADVENTURER 1]
What the hell?!
[ADVENTURER 2]
Hey! Why'd you do that?
Quiet!
Stop your whining
and take a good look
at this so-called man!
[ALL gasp]
[ADVENTURER]
You seein' this?
[COUGAR]
What's going on?
[SHIZU]
A lesser demon.
[low growling]
[KNIGHTS grunting]
You see?
The reason we've isolated
all of you here
is because there's a possibility
that you too have been
possessed by a demon.
I suggest you do as we say
and cooperate.
Should you choose
to do otherwise,
then we'll have no choice
but to see you as a demon
and cut you down.
[SHIZU]
Things are getting ugly.
This isn't good, Shizu.
It looks like these guys
are starting to panic.
Anyone in here could be
a demon in disguise.
Hell, that even includes us.
[SHIZU]
That's true.
Are they wanting us
to fight each other
to figure out
who the demons are?
[MAN laughing]
[ADVENTURER 1]
Who is that?
[ADVENTURER 2]
I've never seen him before.
[laughter continues]
What's with him?
[SHIZU]
I don't know.
But he's strong.
I think he's a mage, but I can't
detect any weaknesses.
Who is this man?
I didn't sense his presence
at all before.
[laughs]
You think you're so clever,
but I'm onto your little game.
You accuse us of being demons
in hopes of
sowing seeds of distrust.
[MINISTER]
Just what are you insinuating?
[DEMON scoffs]
Please excuse me.
It seems the request
is about to be completed
far more easily
than anticipated,
and I found it quite amusing.
Captain of the knights,
I believe you said
that if we do not cooperate
then we'll be seen as demons
and therefore cut down.
So, go on, then.
[KNIGHT CAPTAIN]
Hmm?
I'm saying
that I have no intention
of cooperating with you people.
Nor will I be partaking
in this charade.
[KNIGHT CAPTAIN]
This is not a charade.
It is.
I already know
that you were the one
who summoned the lesser demon.
Shut up! You dare accuse me
of such a thing?
[laughs] You can deflect this
whichever way you like,
but I must say
your efforts are pathetic.
Do you think you can
just ignore our laws?!
[DEMON]
No.
If anything, you've just
saved me a great deal of effort.
[KNIGHT CAPTAIN gasps]
The request stated that we
needed to slay a revived demon.
However, as you've
so aptly demonstrated,
there is no restriction
saying we cannot kill others.
I find this nation's laws
to be quite agreeable.
[SHIZU gasps]
Though I don't believe
we are the only ones
who should face consequences.
Hold on. Are you saying...
[KNIGHT CAPTAIN gasps]
[COUGAR gasps]
[SHIZU]
You there.
Are you planning on slaughtering
everyone here
just to find that demon?
That's the idea.
[SHIZU]
My name is Shizu.
Now, tell me who you are.
-[ALL gasp]
-[DEMON] Well, I go by Black.
It's a sort of nickname given
to me by an old acquaintance.
[SHIZU]
Black.
I will not stand by
and tolerate your actions.
[BLACK laughing]
In that case,
I suppose you'll have to be
the first one to go.
Ha!
[gasps]
[SHIZU] Your flames have
no effect on me.
Yes, so I see.
A superior spirit,
and it identifies with you.
This is a bit of a hassle,
but I can deal with it.
Though, I think I'll toy
with you before I kill you.
[SHIZU]
You can try.
♪
[BLACK chuckles]
[SHIZU yells]
-She's amazing.
-I know.
I guess that's what the power
of a champion looks like.
Be careful.
[SHIZU]
Who are you really?
[BLACK laughs]
Shouldn't you be more focused
on your impending death?
Knowing my origins
will only bring you despair.
Honestly, I don't think
you can handle it!
Just give up.
It doesn't matter who I am.
And it certainly won't help you
win this fight.
[SHIZU]
That may be true.
But regardless, I can't
allow you to run free,
it's far too dangerous.
So be warned,
I'm about to get serious!
[BLACK laughs]
How fun.
[SHIZU] He'll regret
underestimating me.
It's time to end this.
Inferno Flame!
[ALL gasp]
[SHIZU gasps]
Seriously?
[BLACK snickering]
That was excellent.
You're quite remarkable.
I never imagined
that a mere human
could harness Ifrit's power.
It has been a long time since
I've felt this sort of thrill.
[SHIZU]
You are a demon.
Unbelievable.
I can't believe that fire attack
didn't hurt him.
[BLACK]
Oh. I wouldn't go that far.
Her flame attack did hurt,
and I'm actually
in a fair amount of pain.
But that's what makes
this fight interesting.
Now then, I think it's time
that we end this game.
[SHIZU gasps]
[BLACK]
What?!
♪
Impossible.
That mask.
That time compression.
No. Could it be...
Infinity?
I get it.
I can only assume your mask
suppresses time.
To think there's a human
who can use such an item.
[laughs]
You are very intriguing.
On that note,
I think I shall take my leave
for the time being.
[ALL gasp happily]
[ALL cheering]
[ADVENTURER 1]
Well done!
[ADVENTURER 2] Way to show
that demon how it's done!
I would just like to say
for the record
we had no intention of
neglecting any adventurer here.
It was all part of our plan to
lure the demon out from hiding.
[SHIZU] We're lucky
he decided to withdraw.
His strength...
There's no doubt he was
holding back during our fight.
And...
[BLACK scoffs]
It seems the request is about
to be completed
far more easily
than anticipated.
[SHIZU]
Request?
But who would employ
such a powerful demon?
This is bad.
[SHIZU]
Demon Lord Leon once told me
about demons who were known
as the progenitors.
[LEON] These demons
are rather unorthodox,
so they can be
quite troublesome.
And in place of a name,
they're instead referred to
by their signature color.
The Red Progenitor
is known as Rouge.
The White Progenitor, Blanc.
And the Black Progenitor
is called Noir.
[SHIZU]
Black.
Noir.
[chuckles]
It couldn't be.
What reason would he have
to come here?
-[knock on door]
-[SHIZU] Hmm?
[SHIZU]
Come in.
Excuse me.
His Majesty would like
an audience with you.
Would you please accompany me?
[SHIZU]
Of course.
[KNIGHT]
You were truly magnificent
in that fight earlier.
I can't believe the demon
turned tail.
[SHIZU]
I was fortunate that he did.
In truth, I might not have
survived otherwise.
[KNIGHT]
There's no need to be modest.
While it is a shame
he managed to escape,
we still have you here,
and that's very reassuring.
[SHIZU chuckles]
[SHIZU]
Underground?
Isn't this where
the demon's remains are?
This knight.
I don't think I saw him
in the reception hall.
So exactly how did he learn
about my fight
with the demon earlier?
[SHIZU gasps]
[SHIZU]
The minister and the king?
[doors slam shut]
[SHIZU gasps]
Thank you for coming,
Miss Shizu.
As king, I'm grateful
that you would offer
your life for this nation.
That's a very grand gesture.
[SHIZU]
What do you mean?
My, you're slow
to catch on, aren't you?
You must be feeling
utterly exhausted
after fighting that demon.
That's why it would be prudent
to sacrifice you now
before you can recover.
[SHIZU scoffs]
I see.
This was all a conspiracy.
Now you get it.
Feel free to call me Orthos.
[SHIZU gasps]
[SHIZU]
As in the imperial knight
who was hailed as a champion?
That makes sense.
You were never sealed away
at all, were you?
You were a demon
and an enemy of mankind.
[ORTHOS] What's more, I'm also
the current ruler of this land.
[SHIZU]
Your plan was to gather
the best adventurers
and eliminate them,
passing them off as demons.
Then you, a true demon,
would gain more power.
It would seem
that the Kingdom of Filtwood
is ruled by a horde of demons,
and the king is nothing
more than a puppet.
[ORTHOS chuckles]
I watched your fight earlier
through the minister's eyes.
While the demon you fought
was powerful,
he ended up being
a disappointment.
Your mask, though,
now that intrigues me.
It seems to be very valuable,
which means
I should like to own it.
I will drink your blood,
devour your flesh,
and ultimately,
I shall make your power my own.
Doesn't that sound nice?
[SHIZU]
Don't make me laugh.
[laughs]
Oh, please.
Without your magic
at full strength,
you're practically helpless.
You fool.
You can't possibly win.
[SHIZU]
This would have been better
if I had a chance to prepare.
But I have no choice!
♪
[ORTHOS scoffs]
[SHIZU gasps]
Well, it seems you have
some strength left.
If you can injure me,
then you must be even stronger
than the Silver Wings.
[SHIZU]
So you were the one?
Yes, indeed.
Though they both escaped
before I could finish them off.
For you, I shall make things
much more difficult.
-[BOTH snicker]
-[SHIZU gasps]
Did you know,
there are a few different ranks
among the demon race?
I'm the legendary class.
What you would call
a Greater Demon General.
Also known as an Archdemon!
[SHIZU gasps]
[SHIZU groans]
[ORTHOS]
Do you understand now?
As a man-made hero,
the voices
of this nations' people
are what give me power.
And that power is
what afforded me a name,
thus allowing me to become
a named being on my own terms.
Exactly like that supreme being
who reigns up at the top.
[SHIZU]
Wait, what?
[ORTHOS laughs]
[ORTHOS] It's nothing
a human like you
needs to worry about.
-[SHIZU groaning]
-[ORTHOS laughing]
[ORTHOS] This is pathetic,
and here I thought
you were supposed to be
an almighty champion.
[SHIZU choking]
A pity.
You should have let
Ifrit out to play for a bit.
Even though all it would
really do is prolong your death.
-[laughing menacingly]
-[MINISTER laughs]
[KING laughs]
[SHIZU]
I'm out of magic,
but Ifrit still has
some strength left.
If I let it rampage,
it should be enough
to defeat even an Archdemon.
[BLACK]
Giving up so soon?
[ORTHOS]
Huh?
[BLACK] If you're strong enough
to do me harm,
then it would be disappointing
for you to die
at the hands of this weakling.
[SHIZU gasps, coughs]
[SHIZU gasps]
It's you.
[BLACK] It's my policy
to always keep my promises.
[SHIZU gasps]
[BLACK chuckles]
The knight captain!
How?!
Our knights are renowned
for their unrivaled abilities.
I'd hardly dare count
their abilities as "unrivaled."
Lesser demons
aren't that strong.
Then again, it's apparent
that you and I
have vastly different standards
when it comes to power.
[grunts angrily]
You may be a powerful demon
but there's no way you are
a match for the three of us.
After the Conqueror of Flames,
you're next.
Just you wait and see.
[MINSTER gasps]
[KING screaming in fear]
Impossible! But how?
We have the protection
of the Greater Demon General
himself!
-[gasping]
-[flesh tears]
-[SHIZU gasps]
-[ORTHOS grunts]
[BLACK] That's enough
of your squealing, pig.
[SHIZU] I didn't think
that he had actually left
the castle grounds,
but I never expected he'd be
hunting the demons in disguise.
[ORTHOS laughs]
Don't get cocky
because you killed my puppets.
It'll take more than that
to defeat an Archdemon.
A lower demon like you
could never possibly--
[ORTHOS groaning, choking]
Who's the lower demon, exactly?
For a dependent of Red,
you're quite overconfident.
That's why you can't judge
how powerful your opponents are.
[ORTHOS choking]
No, impossible.
You... You can't do this.
[BLACK]
You have disgraced yourself
by aligning
with these lower demons.
You don't deserve
to live anymore.
I think I shall
destroy your soul.
That way there's no possibility
of you ever being revived!
[ORTHOS]
No!
[screaming]
[BLACK chuckles]
[birds chirping]
[RIMURU]
After that, all the demons
in the Kingdom of Filtwood
were purged.
The deaths of
the king and minister
were proclaimed to be the work
of a demon named Black.
And the records indicated
that Shizu was the champion
who destroyed the demon.
Now, as long as you keep
your story straight,
it will save me the trouble
of having to come
after you in the future.
[COUGAR] What was the deal with
that demon named Black anyway?
[SHIZU] I think we're better off
not knowing.
If you say so.
It's like people always say,
"ignorance is a blessing"
or whatever, right?
Well, I'm heading
in this direction.
Take care of yourself, Shizu.
[SHIZU]
I will. Until we meet again.
Well, then...
Perhaps one day
someone will be able to handle
that demon better than I did.
[RIMURU]
And so, time passed.
[BLACK chuckles]
It seems that mask
has appeared again.
I suppose the rumors are true.
And the slime monster,
he's very interesting.
[snickering]
[RIMURU] And even though
the whole thing
was one-sided and silent,
that's how Rimuru and Black
had their first encounter.
Black would later be summoned
by Rimuru himself,
and would receive a new name.
Diablo.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Tales: Veldora's Journal."