♪
[inaudible]
[RIMURU]
Orc Lord, I'm going to end you.
[wind howling]
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[BENIMARU gasps]
[grunts]
[explosion]
[debris clattering]
[RANGA growling]
♪
[RIMURU]
A majin?
[GELMUD]
What's the big idea?
You have some nerve
choosing to interfere
in the great
Lord Gelmud's plans.
[RIMURU]
Gelmud?
[GREAT SAGE]
Gelmud is--
[RIMURU] The dude who named
Rigurd's eldest son, right?
[GREAT SAGE]
Uh, yes.
[GELMUD] A new Demon Lord
who would have done my bidding
was just about to be born,
but now you've gone
and ruined everything!
[RIMURU]
A Demon Lord?
Say what?
[GELMUD]
You heard me!
Why do you think
I gave out so many names?
Sowed so many seeds?
It was all part of my plan
to create the ultimate pawn!
Now I understand.
That's why you attacked us?
And killed our people?
[SHION grunts]
Oh, thank goodness,
that's Lord Gelmud himself.
[LIZARDMAN] That's the guy
who gave Sir Gabiru his name?
[GABIRU]
But why are you here?
Could it be that you've come
to save the lizardmen?
[GELMUD]
Shut up, you stupid lizard!
Why don't you just let
the Orc Lord eat you already?
Huh?
Uh, hey,
what is he talking about?
[GELMUD]
Get it through your head.
You're literally so worthless
that you'll never be
anything more than a nuisance.
But if the Orc Lord eats you,
you'll become
part of his strength.
Take heart in the fact
that at least if you die
you'll finally have served
some sort of purpose.
[whimpers]
Lord Gelmud!
[GELMUD]
Dinner is served, Orc Lord!
[low grunting]
[GELMUD]
What's wrong?
A new Demon Lord will be born?
I don't understand.
[GELMUD]
Ugh. You really are an imbecile.
It's you!
You'll become the Demon Lord,
the Orc Disaster
and rule over
the Forest of Jura.
That has always been the plan,
and it's what
he and I both desire.
[RIMURU]
Who's "he"?
[GELMUD] Why are you
just standing there,
you fat, stupid pig?!
Argh! We're running out of time.
I wasn't supposed to interfere,
but I can see I have no choice!
-Wh... What's he going to do?
-Sir Gabiru!
Get to safety!
[GELMUD]
Die!
-[screaming]
-[LIZARDMAN] Sir Gabiru!
♪
[gasps]
They saved me?
[groaning weakly]
I'm so glad
you didn't get injured.
[weakly]
Thank goodness.
[gasping]
[sobbing]
[screaming]
How could you do this?!
[GELMUD]
I already told you.
You only exist to become fodder
for the Orc Lord.
[gasps]
[GELMUD laughing]
I will show you the strength
of a superior majin.
Now, die!
Deathmarch Dance!
Lord Gelmud!
[explosion]
[electricity crackling]
[GABIRU whimpering]
[gasps]
[GELMUD]
What?
[gasping]
Wow. That was superior?
You can't kill anyone
with that weak sauce move.
[GELMUD nervously]
No. Impossible.
Did you just
step in and save us?
Heads up.
[gasping]
Healing potions.
Use them on your comrades.
Uh, right.
Stay strong.
To think you did this for me.
Thank you.
Now.
[GELMUD groans]
What is this?
[RIMURU]
So this guy was behind it all.
I can't believe
Gabiru was fooled by him.
But I've grown
to kinda like Gabiru.
And that's a good enough reason
to help him out.
[GELMUD] You. How dare you?
Don't you know who I am?!
-[thuds]
-[groans]
[GELMUD gasps]
You'll pay for that.
[groans]
[panting]
You keep on talking like
you're some kinda big shot,
but you seem
pretty pathetic to me.
[GELMUD] Okay, listen.
Why don't you and I team up?
-We'll--
-[groans sharply]
-[grunts]
-[exhales sharply]
[yelling]
Damn you!
You're finished, you hear me?
I'm going to make you
regret this!
You said "he" earlier.
Who was it
you were talking about?
Who's the real mastermind?
[GELMUD]
Eh... No. Leave me alone.
Hey, Orc Lord, do something!
I'm so very hungry.
[GELMUD]
Who cares?!
Just help me, Orc Lord.
Uh... I mean, Geld.
[ORC LORD gasps]
[GELMUD]
I shall name you Geld.
Geld, huh?
[GELMUD] One day,
you will take possession
of the Great Forest of Jura,
and become the Orc Disaster.
[ORC LORD]
Hmm.
[GELMUD]
Just hurry up and evolve
into a Demon Lord, stupid.
[gasps]
[GELMUD] Oh, look,
the mountain of lard
finally decided to move.
[laughing menacingly]
Oh, You're in for it now,
you'll regret messing with me.
Get them, Geld.
Make them rue the day
they interfered with my plan.
-[RANGA gasps]
-[SHION gasps]
[GREAT SAGE] It appears
Gelmud's life signs have ceased.
Uh, yeah, that's pretty obvious.
[bones crunching]
[chewing noisily]
[RIMURU]
He's eating Gelmud.
[growling]
[GREAT SAGE] Confirmed.
The Orc Lord, Geld's,
magicules have
drastically increased.
Evolution to Demon Lord
has commenced.
[gasps]
♪
[GREAT SAGE]
Successful.
Geld has evolved
into the Demon Lord
known as the Orc Disaster.
Well, that's not good.
This just got harder.
Guess we should
do something about him.
[roaring]
I am the great Orc Disaster.
And I am the one that will
devour all in this world!
My name is Geld.
Geld, the new Demon Lord!
[RIMURU] If I don't do something
to stop him,
it really will be a disaster.
♪
-Shion.
-Right.
I'm on it.
Whoa, hey.
Allow us to handle the pig.
[SHION]
You call yourself a Demon Lord?
That's some ego!
Now, prepare to die!
[grunts]
-[ORC LORD yells]
-[grunts]
♪
[grunts]
[slice]
[RIMURU]
They did it.
[HAKUROU gasps]
[gasps]
His healing abilities
are insane.
[SOUEI]
Arcane Thread Fetters.
[ORC LORD]
Hmm.
Do it. Finish him!
Take this, you foul swine!
♪
[howling]
[explosion]
Outta magicules?
[RANGA]
Forgive me.
-Rest in my shadow.
-[RANGA] Right.
Uh... What the...
[ALL gasp]
He's alive?
So this is what pain feels like.
Seriously?
My Lord, I offer
my body up to you.
All right.
♪
[bones crunching]
[chewing noisily]
[grunting]
[energy humming]
Self-regeneration
and healing magic?
More food. I'm still hungry!
I need even more power!
Give it to me!
[gasps]
My lord.
Don't worry, I've got this.
[RIMURU] After all,
I have a trick up my sleeve.
Though it's a bit cowardly.
You're up, Great Sage.
I'm counting on you.
Defeat the Orc Disaster!
[GREAT SAGE]
Understood.
Switching over
to autopilot mode.
♪
[RIMURU] It's time to see
what Great Sage is capable of.
Devour him!
Chaos Eater!
♪
[RIMURU]
Sweet moves.
I knew I could
count on you, Great Sage.
[ORC LORD]
Impossible.
♪
Hmm.
[grunts]
No, my lord!
[ORC LORD yelling]
I'm done playing around!
I will devour you!
[grunting]
♪
[evil laughter]
I think you're going to be
rather tasty.
[ORC LORD screaming]
[RIMURU]
Flare circle. It's over.
[screaming continues]
[GREAT SAGE]
Operation complete.
[RIMURU]
Awesome work, Great Sage.
That went perfectly.
[ORC LORD continues screaming]
[RIMURU]
And yet...
[laughing]
[GREAT SAGE]
Notice: An error has occurred.
[RIMURU]
Just my luck.
The dude's got
fire resistance.
Not that I can say
I'm surprised.
[GREAT SAGE]
An emergency has arisen.
[RIMURU]
I'll take over.
-[GREAT SAGE] Uh...
-[RIMURU] It's nothing personal.
In fact, it's because of you
that I think I might know
how to beat him.
So, just leave the rest
of this fight to me, partner.
[laughs]
It would appear your fire
has no effect on me.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, true that.
But in the end,
you may have preferred
the burning to death route.
[ORC LORD scoffs]
You've proved to be
a worthy opponent.
So get ready, 'cause I'm about
to take you on for real.
[laughs]
Is that so?
Then are you saying
you weren't serious before?
There's no way you could
ever hope to defeat me.
Just give up
and let me eat you.
[RIMURU]
I'd be terrible for your diet.
I think I'll eat you instead.
You see, I'm a slime.
[grunting]
Why, you...
[RIMURU] I'm sorry, did you
think you were the only dude
who could eat things?
Will you be able
to eat me first?
[grunting]
[RIMURU] Or will I be able
to eat you first?
First one to consume
the other, wins!
[ORC LORD screaming]
[ORC LORD grunting]
[RIMURU]
It's between his "Starved"
and my "Predator."
Which skill is stronger?
The winner has to be "Predator."
Because if he is starved,
then I'm...
a devourer!
♪
[ORC CHILDREN crying]
Are you hungry, young ones?
Wait just a moment.
[bone cracking]
[moans sadly]
[ORC LORD]
Here. Eat it.
[ORC CHILDREN chomping]
[ORC LORD] I want you to grow up
to be big and strong.
[ORC GENERAL]
My king, please don't do this.
In this famine,
if we were to lose you,
our esteemed leader,
then there would be nothing left
for our people
but hopeless misery.
The child born two days ago,
died today.
And the one born yesterday
is at death's door.
No matter what, my body will
always regenerate its parts.
But if this isn't
a state of hopeless misery,
then what else is it?
My king.
[ORC LORD] I'll go to the forest
and search for food.
But the Storm Dragon.
The Forest of Jura
is under his protection.
[ORC LORD] The Storm Dragon
has been sealed away
for a long time.
Our people can't afford
to wait any longer.
I'm so hungry.
I want to eat something.
Anything.
[groaning]
[GELMUD] I think I shall
give you a name and some food.
Who are you?
[GELMUD]
I am Gelmud.
If you like,
just think of me as your father.
[ORC LORD] He told me
that as the Orc Lord,
anyone I ate would not die,
rather they'd simply be
under the effects of "Starved."
I was just another pawn
in his evil scheme.
But I had to take the risk.
That is why
I must constantly eat.
Even if you are a slime
that can eat anything,
I cannot allow myself
to be devoured.
[RIMURU] I have the advantage
when it comes to eating.
You will lose.
[ORC LORD] I ate all
the monsters I encountered.
I ate Lord Gelmud.
I ate my own brethren.
Still, my people are starving.
So, I can't afford
to lose to you.
[RIMURU] In this world,
it's eat or be eaten.
You lost to me,
so you're going to die now.
[ORC LORD] I told you,
I can't afford to lose.
If I die, then my sins
will fall upon my people.
It doesn't matter
if I'm sinful.
I'd do anything to keep them
from starving.
I'll carry the whole
world's hunger if I have to.
[RIMURU] Even so,
you're still going to die.
But you can rest easy.
Because I'll devour you
and your sins.
[ORC LORD]
You're going to eat my sins?
[RIMURU]
Yes, and not just yours.
I'll eat the sins
of all your people.
[ORC LORD] You think you can
devour all of them?
Really?
You must be very greedy.
[RIMURU]
You're right. I am greedy.
♪
[birds chirping]
[gasps]
[CHILDREN laughing]
[crying]
How can you be so greedy?
To just eat
all of our sins like that.
Thank you.
My hunger has finally
been sated.
[GREAT SAGE]
Confirmed.
The Orc Disaster is gone.
♪
Now you can rest in peace,
Lord Geld.
With the Orc Lord
finally defeated,
the effects of Starved
also vanished.
In that moment,
the war with the orc army ended.
[cheering]
[GOBTA]
Woo-hoo!
My king.
I'm so happy
you're finally free.
♪
Well, it's over.
Yes.
[RIMURU]
I made you guys a promise.
That you'd be free once
we defeated the orcs.
I appreciate your help.
My lord, I have a request.
What's up?
Would you please accept
our continued allegiance?
In the end, we would all prefer
to keep serving under you.
Are you sure?
Yes, it would be
an honor for us.
After all, my lord,
we're fortunate to have met you.
[RIMURU grunts]
And I am your secretary
and bodyguard, remember?
So it looks like
you're stuck with me.
[BENIMARU]
We will serve you, always.
[RIMURU]
Okay. Cool.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"The Jura Forest Alliance."