So it looks as though
the Eastern Empire
has decided to stay put.
For now.
At least there's that.
Our intelligence bureau
will continue to monitor them.
More importantly, how did it
go in the Forest of Jura?
Not only did it go terribly,
but it kinda seems
like you don't care
that we managed to make
it back in one piece.
Give me your report.
It sounds like you
care more about
that stupid report than us.
The only thing I want
is a hot bath.
I don't know what the heck
you two are complaining about.
I'm the poor sap who had
to listen you guys argue
the entire time
we were traveling.
[growls]
[gasps] So, uh...
[clears throat]
Anyway, we searched the whole
cave like you requested.
And Veldora's
definitely gone, sir.
We weren't able to find
a single thing.
It's empty?
There's nothing there.
[sighs]
Thank you for your
report on the cave.
Righty-o, we'll get
outta your hair.
[FUZE]
I'll give you three days off.
[ALL gasp]
Then I'll need you to
investigate the areas
around the forest.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Keep an eye out for monsters.
They'll be more active
with Veldora gone.
Report any changes,
no matter how small.
Be thorough.
Search every nook and cranny.
You're excused.
He is such an ass!
"You're excused," he says,
like we should be grateful
for three lousy days off
when we're so exhausted
he doesn't even know!
You all talk a big game,
but I bet you'd never
say those things
to the guild master's face.
[KAVAL, EREN shouting]
[KAVAL, EREN sigh]
Do we have to go back there?
I guess.
If Fuze gives an order,
then you gotta do it.
[EREN]
I just want a break.
[SHIZU]
Excuse me.
[EREN, GIDO]
Huh?
You need somethin' or what?
[SHIZU] Did you just say
that you're going
to the Forest of Jura?
[KAVAL]
And what if we did?
[SHIZU] Would you allow me to
accompany you on your journey?
[KAVAL]
Hmm.
Sure thing!
Uh! Excuse you?
Last I checked, I'm the leader,
so I'll be the one
who says yea or nay.
Oh, come on.
It'll be lots more fun
with another companion along.
Eren.
That's Kaval and Gido.
[SHIZU]
Shizu.
We're happy to have you, Shizu.
Fine.
We're leaving here
in three days.
If that's good for you,
then you can join us.
[EREN giggles]
[SHIZU]
Thank you.
[RIMURU]
Ready, Ranga?
Check out my new move.
[RANGA]
I shall.
[RIMURU]
Rimuru, transform!
And now,
Black Lightning!
[RIMURU]
Whoa!
[RIMURU] I didn't expect my new
skill to be quite that powerful.
Note to self:
Be careful about using
this one in public places.
[RANGA]
Black Lightning.
You are truly amazing, master!
[sighs]
[RIMURU]
Everything's so peaceful.
[RIMURU] Yep. Looks like
things are going great.
[RIMURU]
A few weeks had passed
since Rimuru and his party
have returned with Kaijin
and the other Dwarves.
As they say, "Strike while
the iron's hot."
[laughing]
[RIMURU] The village now has
a gifted blacksmith, Kaijin.
[RIMURU] The oldest of the
three Dwarf brothers, Garm,
was now acting as
the town's armor smith.
And that's why we tan the hides,
so they're even more durable.
[RIMURU]
The middle brother, Dord,
taught everyone his
superb crafting techniques.
[RIMURU] While the youngest
and quietest brother, Myrd,
became the town's
new resident architect.
[RIMURU] With their guidance,
Rimuru and the Goblins
were well on their way
to building a village
that was guaranteed to thrive.
[RIMURU] Man, I'm still
not over the surprise
we had waiting for us
when we got back from Dwargon.
[RIMURU] Uh, Rigurd,
who are these Goblins?
They all heard
the rumors about you,
so they've journeyed here
from other nearby villages
to seek your divine protection.
[RIMURU]
Oh. Cool.
[GOBLINS] Lord Rimuru,
we're so happy you're back!
[RIMURU]
Yo, Great Sage,
exactly how many
new Goblins are there?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer: Around 500.
[RIMURU]
What?! Ugh...
Maybe it would be better
if I asked them all to leave.
Uh... What'll happen
if they don't stay?
[GREAT SAGE]
With the disappearance
of Veldora the Storm Dragon,
Orcs, Lizardmen, Ogres,
and the other intelligent
monster races
are vying for dominance
in the Great Forest of Jura.
The unevolved Goblins
will likely be eliminated.
[RIMURU]
Not what I wanted to hear.
[RIMURU] All right.
You're all welcome to stay.
[GOBLINS cheering]
[RIMURU]
So, Rimuru sucked it up
and named all 500
of the newcomers.
Then spent another three
days in sleep mode.
[RIMURU] I was worried
about how it'd work out,
but I think everyone'll be able
to live here just fine.
Way to kill it, Kaijin.
'Kay. I'll show you all how
it's done, so pay attention.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[GOBTA grunting]
Ha!
[RIMURU]
Whoa! He summoned one?
[GOBLINS gasp]
And that's all it takes,
so why don't you guys
give it a try now?
[chuckles]
[RIMURU]
Gobta is teaching the others
how to summon their
Tempest Wolf partners.
[RIMURU] I can't believe
he's good at something.
[GOBTA muttering]
[RIMURU] Back when Rimuru
almost accidentally left
Gobta behind in Dwargon...
...the lazy Goblin prayed for
help with all his might.
Until...
[gasps]
[RIMURU] ...he managed
to summon his wolf!
He then rode his furry steed
straight out of the kingdom.
Where he rejoined Rimuru's party
and made it back home
relatively safe and sound.
[RIMURU] Looks like Gobta
can achieve great things
when he puts his mind to it.
[RIMURU] In that moment,
Rimuru's opinion of Gobta
improved considerably.
No, that won't work at all.
You've gotta make
more of a "ungh" sound.
And poof! There they'll be.
[GOBLINS]
Hmm?
[RIMURU] He's not exactly
the best teacher, though.
[RIMURU] In that moment,
Rimuru's opinion of Gobta
dropped considerably.
[RIGURD]
Lord Rimuru!
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
Rigurd?
After the new arrivals,
Rigurd was promoted from
Goblin Lord to Goblin King.
He's in charge of leading
all the other village elders
who joined them.
They sort of threw
the job at him.
[RIMURU]
I can't be sure,
but it almost seems like
becoming the Goblin King
made him evolve a bit more.
[RIGURD chuckles]
[RIMURU]
What's up, my guy?
Sir, we've just
received a message
from the security team.
It says they've spotted
suspicious beings in the forest.
[RIMURU]
Monsters?
No. Humans, my lord.
[RIMURU]
Humans?!
Yes, it's possible
that they're scouts
sent here from another nation
to expand their dominion.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
[EREN cries]
This whole mess
is your fault, Kaval!
What kind of idiot goes around
stabbing giant ants nests?
Shut up and show your leader
some respect, dammit!
No, you haven't earned
my respect!
If I die today, I swear that
I'm coming back to haunt you!
[laughing]
Well, come on, Eren,
that's not even possible,
and do you wanna know why?
Because I'm gonna
be dead with you!
[EREN screaming]
Shizu, no!
Let's go!
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasping]
[gasps]
Wow, she's so strong.
[gasps] Quick, behind you!
Do something!
[EREN]
Shizu!
Are you okay?
[SHIZU]
Yes.
No way. Was that magic?
It kinda looked like
Black Lightning.
[RIMURU] Man, Black Lighting
really is boss-level stuff.
I'd better shelf it after all.
[ALL]
It's a slime?
[RIMURU] Yep. You got a
problem with slimes?
Uh, no.
I just never heard one talk.
It's kind of hard to believe.
[RIMURU] Here, I think
this belongs to you.
I hope I didn't hurt you
with my Lightning Skill.
Nuh-uh. I'm all right.
[RIMURU] I met her
sooner than I expected.
[chuckles]
You saved me, thank you.
[RIMURU]
My destiny.
So, how are our guests?
[RIGURD]
Well...
[KAVAL]
What the hell?!
I already called dibs
on that meat.
--[RIMURU] Huh?
--[EREN] Back off, jerk.
[EREN] I cooked this piece
myself, so you can go hungry.
[GIDO]
Both of you shut up.
Besides if anybody's eating
that, it's gonna be me.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
It's all my fault.
They said they were starving,
so I gave them some food.
[RIMURU]
Don't feel bad, Rigurd.
Helping people in need
is a good thing,
I'm proud of you, man.
You honor me with
your praise, my lord.
In that case, I will dedicate
myself to helping others.
[RIMURU]
Attaboy.
[RIGUR]
Lord Rimuru. After you.
[RIMURU]
Actually, I feel like
I've seen these guys
somewhere before.
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer:
They are the trio you saw
in Veldora's cave.
[RIMURU]
Right, the idiots.
She ate through her mask?
Now that's what I call a skill.
My apologies.
I fear we have little
to offer you,
but we welcome you
as our honored guests.
Please allow me
to make introductions.
Here. May I present to you
the master of our village,
the Great Lord Rimuru!
[ALL]
The master?
[RIMURU]
Got a problem with that?
Uh, no, not at all.
We knew that you weren't
an ordinary slime,
but it's so shocking.
[RIMURU]
They seem a little overwhelmed.
I need to figure out how to
show them I'm actually friendly.
[RIMURU]
Nice to meet you!
My name is Rimuru the Slime!
I'm not a bad slime, slurp.
[SHIZU snickers]
Something wrong?
[RIMURU] Hold up, did she
understand that reference?
[KAVAL]
Forgive our rudeness.
It's just that we thought
we were done for back there,
and we never expected
to be rescued by a monster.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, and thanks a lot
for feeding us, too.
Everything's really delicious.
We appreciate your hospitality.
The last thing we expected
to find here
were a bunch of Goblins
building a village.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
She sure is quiet.
[RIMURU] So, why exactly
are you guys in the forest?
The name's Kaval,
not that it's saying much,
but I'm the leader
of this party.
Back there...
My name's Eren.
And you can call me Gido.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
While she's not
a permanent party member,
this girl is tagging
along with us
since we were going
the same way.
[SHIZU]
Shizu.
[RIMURU] So the one
I'm destined to be with
is called "Shizu"?
She's gotta be from Japan,
too. Look how she sits.
[RIMURU]
And?
Well, our boss,
who is this cranky old guy,
ordered us to come here.
[RIMURU]
Kaval told me their entire plan,
because you can obviously
trust a random slime
you found in the forest.
A guild master in Blumund,
one of the kingdoms that borders
the Great Forest of Jura,
had asked them to investigate
the monster activity
in the area.
[RIMURU]
Oh, I see.
Looks like Veldora's absence
is having a greater effect
than I imagined.
Especially if people are
being sent to check out
not just the cave,
but the whole forest, too.
[RIMURU] Well, as you can
see all we're doing here
is building a Goblin village.
So, uh, you don't think
that'll be a problem
with the guild, do you?
Uh, I don't think so.
It should be fine.
And I don't think the guild
has any say in it.
But I'm not sure
about the country.
Hmm. To be honest,
I have no idea.
[RIMURU] Okay. No worries,
we'll figure it out.
You can stay the
night if you want.
Our village is your village.
[ALL]
Thank you so much.
[RIMURU]
Take care of them.
[BOTH]
Right.
[RIMURU]
Do you have a minute?
I wanted to ask you something.
Um, are you from--?
[SHIZU]
That line you said.
It was from a game, right?
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[SHIZU]
"I'm not a bad slime, slurp."
[chuckles nervously]
[SHIZU]
I've never played it,
but I heard about it
from someone else
who's from my country.
[RIMURU]
Yeah!
[RIMURU] I've been closer to
boobs way more as a slime
than I ever was as a human dude.
Talk about your perks.
[SHIZU]
Are you from Japan, as well?
[RIMURU]
Yep.
I see.
I'm glad I met you.
So tell me, how did you
come to this world?
[RIMURU]
I got stabbed to death.
Very heroically, of course.
[SHIZU]
That's terrible.
[RIMURU] And then it was
wham, bam, slime I am.
Ah, so you were reincarnated
into this world.
I'm sure that was
very difficult for you.
[RIMURU]
Was it different for you?
Yes, a bit.
I'm what you call a Summon.
[RIMURU]
Sounds familiar.
That's right,
Veldora mentioned it.
[VELDORA] It requires more than
30 mages performing a ritual
that lasts several days
to bring someone here.
The Summon is expected to
perform as a powerful weapon.
They use magic to carve a curse
into the Summon's soul.
That way they can never
defy their master.
[RIMURU] Wait. Does that
mean Shizu's a weapon?
And that she's cursed?
I am curious, but it'd probably
be rude for me to ask.
[RIMURU] So, when were you
summoned to this world?
A while ago.
There was fire.
The town was burning.
[RIMURU]
A war?
[SHIZU]
Bombs were falling from the sky.
[RIMURU]
The air raids.
My mother and I tried to get
to safety, but then she...
[RIMURU]
What happened to her?
Did she make it?
[SHIZU]
Mm-mmm.
[RIMURU] I know. Do you
wanna see something cool?
[SHIZU]
Oh? Like what?
[RIMURU] Great Sage, I'd like
to use Thought Communication
to show Shizu
some of my memories.
[GREAT SAGE]
Commencing.
[RIMURU]
Check this out!
[gasps]
[SHIZU]
An Elf?
[RIMURU screams]
[RIMURU]
Don't look!
It's not what you
think, I swear!
She's very pretty.
[RIMURU] Ignore that,
and look at this instead.
[gasps]
Amazing.
It reminds me
of New York City.
I saw it on a postcard once.
[RIMURU] After the war ended,
peace came to Japan.
The towns and economy
all flourished.
That's great.
I'm so glad.
I wish my mother
could have seen this.
[RIMURU]
It may be a long shot,
but I wanna make this a world
where everyone can
live in peace, too.
I see.
I hope it really happens.
[RIMURU]
It will, I'm sure of it.
[SHIZU chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[RIMURU]
Uh, Shizu?
[SHIZU sighs]
[SHIZU]
I'm sorry.
[RIMURU]
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Thank you.
[KAIJIN]
Hey, Rimuru.
Can I get your expert
opinion on something?
We need to talk to you about
where to build a new house.
[RIMURU]
Sure. Bye.
[SHIZU]
Bye.
[KAIJIN]
Were you two busy?
[RIMURU]
Shut up!
[KAIJIN]
I think you're blushing.
[RIMURU]
I am not.
[KAIJIN]
Lookin' kinda red.
[PEOPLE screaming]
[screams]
[SHIZU]
Mommy!
Please, Mommy!
[gasps]
Great, another failure.
[SHIZU]
Please.
Help me.
I thought she would be useless,
but perhaps she has
an affinity for fire.
[gasps]
[LEON] Ifrit, I'm offering
her body to you.
Use it well.
[SHIZU gasps]
[snarls]
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Conqueror of Flames."