Okay, I'm ready.
-Right!
[BOTH grunting]
[sword swishes]
[PEOPLE murmuring]
You're the greatest,
Master Hakurou!
Just look at how neat
those fillets are!
[laughing]
Oh, come now, it was
a simple enough task!
Who's ready for dinner?
-It's so light.
-[metallic cling]
Yet still sturdy.
This could be very useful.
Yeah, it'll be great
for weapons.
Or maybe a shield!
Heck, we could even work it
into some armor.
And it's perfect
for accessories, too.
-I bet they'd sell for a lot.
-Uh-huh.
[bubbling]
I'm telling you, Sir Geld,
those were some impressive
fighting skills!
I could learn a lot
from a guy like you.
If anything, I think you were
the impressive one, Gabiru!
You were unstoppable out there!
No, you were impressive!
You were impressive-er!
[BOTH laughing]
No, you're both impressive-est!
[RIMURU] With Charybdis gone
from the skies,
peace returned once again
to the city of Rimuru.
And since Demon Lord Carrion
agreed to a non-aggression pact,
the Jura Tempest Federation
will be guaranteed peace
and stability for a long time.
♪
[RIMURU]
Man.
After a battle like that,
I am one tired slime.
You were awesome
out there, Milim.
Thanks for your help.
Oh, it was my pleasure!
It was almost too easy,
but feel free
to keeping praising me.
I think you were amazing, too,
Rimuru!
You know, it's never too late
to change your mind
and become
a full-fledged Demon Lord!
[RIMURU]
I'm good.
I already told you
I'm not interested.
Is there any merit to being one?
What's that mean?
[RIMURU] Like why did you become
a Demon Lord?
Uh...
I wonder.
Did something bad happen?
Maybe that's why.
[RIMURU]
Why are you asking me?
Good point!
Guess I can't remember.
It was so long ago
I totally forgot.
-[RIMURU] Okay.
-Oh, yeah!
-There is a merit!
-[RIMURU gasps]
-[MILIM grunts]
-[EREN chuckles]
[RIMURU screaming]
[MILIM]
If I wasn't a Demon Lord,
I'd have never made friends
with you!
[RIMURU]
Yeah. True.
[giggles]
[ALL chuckle]
This has all been fun.
But I should probably
get back to work.
What work?
Do you mean right now?
[RIMURU]
Seems kinda sudden.
Come on, it's not like
I'm saying goodbye forever,
you know!
It's just for a little bit.
-Transform!
-[magic humming]
Ta-da!
-[ALL] Oh!
-[RIMURU coughs]
Leave everything to me.
I'll be sure to tell
the other Demon Lords
not to mess with this place,
so no need to worry!
[RIMURU] You're going to see
the other Demon Lords?
Uh-huh!
That's what I just said.
[RIMURU] Be careful,
don't let them trick you.
Yes, don't let them trick you.
Don't let them trick you.
Please don't let those guys
trick you.
Do not let them trick you.
You all need to learn to relax.
Besides, they can't trick me.
I'm way too smart for 'em!
-[MILIM laughs]
-[RIMURU groans]
[MILIM]
Well, I'm off! Fwoosh!
[RIMURU]
Hey, Milim!
And she's gone.
She sure is a free spirit,
isn't she?
Well, that's just how
Lady Milim is.
I'll be looking forward
to her return.
[RIMURU sighs]
[crickets chirping]
[RIMURU groaning]
-[inaudible]
-[distant laughter]
[SHIZU]
Please, save them.
The children.
Hurry.
Please hurry.
♪
[RIMURU]
Huh?
♪
That dream.
It felt so real.
Was it Shizu's regret?
And because of that,
I decided to become
an instructor.
[RIMURU]
Sounds like fun.
I was a teacher at a school.
[RIMURU]
Whoa!
There are schools here?
[SHIZU] Yes, in the Kingdom
of Ingrassia.
I taught kids from other worlds.
[RIMURU]
The Kingdom of Ingrassia, huh?
Oh.
♪
[RIMURU]
There's Benimaru.
Kaijin.
Rigur.
The Goblin Riders.
Geld.
Rigurd.
And heck, even Gabiru.
Things should be safe
in their hands
if I decide to do
some traveling.
♪
[RIMURU] That's why I need to go
to the Kingdom of Ingrassia
as soon as possible.
I think those kids were one
of the reasons
why Shizu was traveling
to see Demon Lord Leon.
So it's up to me
to help them now.
I understand where
you're coming from, My Lord.
Although...
If anything were
to happen to you,
then the Jura Forest Alliance
could be ripped up
from its roots.
Things are just now starting
to take off for us.
[RANGA]
Don't worry, I'll accompany him.
Surely that should give you
some comfort.
[RIMURU]
It'll be fine.
Besides, I'm counting on you
to work together
and keep this place safe.
Just go about your business
as usual, okay?
[ALL]
Sir!
[RIMURU]
All right, I'm off.
Right. Be careful.
We'll all be here
awaiting your return!
Sir Gabiru's so sensitive!
Just let it all out, sir!
[RIMURU]
This is gettin' weird.
I'll be back in no time.
Please don't stay away too long,
Lord Rimuru.
I'll pray for your safe return.
[RIMURU]
Peace!
[ALL]
Safe travels!
[ALL chattering indistinctly]
[RIMURU]
And with that, I was on my way.
In the two years since I was
reincarnated into this world,
this would be the first time
I visited a human kingdom.
♪
The Kingdom of Ingrassia lies
to the west of our nation.
It's also home to the HQ
of the organization
set up to help adventurers.
Fuze told me about it.
Apparently, the location
is sort of in the center
of all the nations.
The kids I'm searching for
are in a place
called Freedom Academy,
a school that was established
by one of Shizu's students.
His name is Yuuki Kagurazaka.
I think he might be Japanese,
so my plan is
to go meet him first.
Fuze wrote me a letter
of introduction,
so hopefully there
won't be any problems.
♪
Thanks to Ranga, we arrived at
the royal capital of Ingrassia
in just three days.
You should probably hang out
in my shadow.
I don't want anyone in the city
to freak out if they see you.
[RANGA]
Great idea, Master.
Feel free to call on me
at any time.
Be careful.
Right.
♪
[RIMURU] Getting into
the capital involves
a strict
identification policy.
Just in case there was
a magical barrier
to prevent monsters
from entering,
I wore the magic-suppressing
mask that Shizu left behind.
Somehow I doubt they'd take
kindly to monsters.
Better safe than sorry.
Fuze was kind enough
to prepare an ID for me,
so getting through security
was actually kind of a breeze.
[PEOPLE chattering]
[RIMURU sighs]
[RIMURU grunts]
Sorry.
It's so crowded.
Our little town
just doesn't compare.
This place is huge.
Whoa, seriously?
Is that glass?
♪
There's no doubt that
this is definitely
the biggest pane of glass
I've seen
since coming to this world.
♪
Is that a church?
Wait.
I'm pretty sure churches and
monsters don't jive or whatever.
It'd probably be smart
to avoid it for right now.
[gasps]
Hey, there's
the Free Union Headquarters.
♪
Lots of glass here, too.
They must be loaded.
♪
[door whooshes]
[gasps]
Automatic doors?
♪
[RECEPTIONIST] I have verified
your letter of introduction.
[RIMURU grunts]
With that, the Grandmaster
has agreed to meet with you.
Right this way.
Just follow me.
[RIMURU]
Okay.
[whooshing]
[RIMURU]
We're teleporting?
I bet they're worried
about spies and stuff.
He should be with you
in just a moment.
[door closes]
[RIMURU]
Huh.
I wonder what this
Grandmaster dude is like?
Thank you for waiting.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the Grandmaster here,
[trailing off]
Yuuki Kagurazaka...
[huffs]
[RIMURU]
It's nice to meet you, too.
I'm Rimuru Tempest.
I'm the leader of
the Jura Tempest Federation,
a nation in the Forest of Jura
that's made up of monsters.
That's Shizu's mask.
Why are you wearing it?
[RIMURU]
Well then,
this makes things kinda awkward.
Let's start with the fact
that I'm a slime
who can mimic the appearance
of any monster I eat.
You "eat?"
What are you saying?
[grunts]
[rumbling, clattering]
Listen to me.
[growling]
I'm not a bad slime, slurp.
[YUUKI gasps]
What'd you say?
You know, I also played
that game.
You told Shizu about it, right?
Please continue.
You have my attention.
It's a long story.
Man, really?
I can't believe that's how
that show ended!
Belldandy is
my favorite character!
-[YUUKI sniggers]
-[RIMURU laughs]
Is there anything else
you'd like to know about?
By the time I got stabbed
and reincarnated,
I'd already finished
most of the anime and manga
you probably know of.
Naturally, I have it
all committed to memory.
I'm a sucker for a good story.
I mean, what guy isn't?
You are like
the coolest dude ever!
Thank you for sharing
your knowledge with me!
Now, let's talk games.
What FF are they up to
these days?
We're on 19.
Holy crap.
And?
The Sagrada Familia
is almost finished.
Really? You're kidding!
Iitomo ended.
Oh no, why?
Why on earth would they end such
a sacred and wholesome show?
BomBom shut down.
No!
But I looked forward to those
comics every month as a kid!
Hey! What about that one series,
Glass Ma--
It's still going.
For real?
Then Five Star--
Technically, each book has
its own ending, so...
So, it's still going?
Honestly, I'd love to know
how it all ends, myself.
You wanna know about
the prime ministers?
-Nah. Not interested.
-[RIMURU groans]
[YUUKI sighs]
Anyway, that's awesome.
I'm so happy.
Hearing about all this stuff
has been amazing.
Still though, I wish I could
have seen it with my own eyes.
Your own eyes.
Huh.
Got any paper?
[YUUKI]
Uh, sure.
-Give me a sec.
-Huh?
Transform!
Oh! I'm guessing this must be
your actual form.
[gulps]
[ding]
[RIMURU]
Here's a whole volume.
Whoa!
You have to tell me what kind of
magic you used to make this!
[RIMURU laughs]
That's a trade secret.
I actually just used
Great Sage's ability
to the fullest.
I just had to copy memories
of the things I've read
onto the paper I ate.
[GREAT SAGE] Notice.
This is a waste of my ability.
[RIMURU] It's not! This is the
best thing you've ever done,
and don't you dare say
otherwise!
Well, you should go get
some more paper
if you wanna know
what happens next.
[YUUKI chuckles]
[ding]
[YUUKI]
This is the best day ever.
-Thank you!
-[RIMURU laughs]
So Yuuki, have I finally
convinced you
that I'm not a bad slime?
You're cool with me!
[inhales sharply]
The news about Shizu
is sad to hear,
but I do trust you.
Thank you for these. Looks like
I have a lot to catch up on.
Now then,
why did you come to see me?
Are you trying to find a way
back to our world?
Maybe?
No, it's not that.
Wait, is that even possible?
[YUUKI exhales]
[RIMURU]
I guess if it was,
you would have done it
a long time ago.
I've given up on that idea.
My body was probably
cremated anyway.
Yeah, that would make things
more difficult.
But honestly,
it doesn't make it
impossible, either.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Think about it.
Japan has a lot of stories
regarding monsters.
Things like ogres and demons
appear in legends
all across the world.
And I figure that if some sort
of condition is met,
then moving between our worlds
should be possible.
Right?
[RIMURU]
Yeah, maybe.
So if your goal isn't
to go back,
then why are you here?
All in all, I'm pretty happy
with the life
I have in this new world.
I've built a town,
and I just want it to be
a safe place
for me and my friends.
But still, there is
something bothering me.
Oh, and what's that?
Shizu's regret.
♪
Now I get it.
When you say regret,
do you mean the children
from Freedom Academy?
Because I could see
that being her dying wish.
Okay then.
Rimuru,
I'm willing to entrust
Shizu's students to you.
[RIMURU] Yuuki arranged
for me to be a teacher
at the school
where the kids were at.
Meaning that I would take over
teaching them in place of Shizu.
The cool thing is, the job comes
with a dorm for teachers
along with three meals a day!
The daily wage is
ten silver coins.
Not too shabby!
[footsteps]
[YUUKI]
Hey, Rimuru,
do you know
about Hinata Sakaguchi?
The name sounds familiar.
I see.
She was also
a student of Shizu's.
Oh. That girl.
I'm pretty sure Shizu said
she left or something?
That's right.
Back when she was in her prime,
Shizu had complete control
over the fire spirit
known as Ifrit.
But Hinata was able
to gain strength
that surpassed Shizu's
when she was just 15.
-That's cool.
-It sure is.
And it should tell you
how much power she possesses.
[RIMURU] Nope, not really,
so I'll just act like I know.
[YUUKI] You're probably
wondering why I even brought
Hinata up to start with.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[YUUKI] I just want you to know
there's a difference
between Otherworlders like you,
me, and Hinata,
who came here by accident,
and those five students.
Because they're Summons.
Wait, "Summons"?
[RIMURU]
Veldora mentioned that.
A Summon?
Is that supposed to be different
from an Otherworlder?
[VELDORA] It requires
more than 30 mages
performing a ritual
that lasts several days
to bring someone here.
The Summon is expected
to perform as a powerful weapon.
[RIMURU]
A weapon?
[VELDORA]
Yes, for the Summoner.
They use magic to carve a curse
into the Summon's soul.
That way, they can never
defy their master.
Summons are typically
brought here
to serve a specific purpose.
Which means, they are given
a power to suit that purpose.
Usually, because it's possible,
they'll become a Hero
and serve
as mankind's trump card.
When crossing between worlds,
the person is given
a body to use.
At that time, the body takes in
a massive amount of energy
and begins to acquire
new abilities.
And sometimes, a child ends up
being the one who's summoned.
And when the amount of energy
that comes with it
ends up being more than what
their growing body can handle,
the body will eventually be
incinerated by that energy
because it has no place to go.
[RIMURU gasps]
Hold the phone.
What's this have to do
with those five school kids?
That's what I'm trying
to explain.
Those kids are Summons.
Wait, so are they gonna be okay?
I'm not sure yet.
They came when different nations
failed to summon a Hero.
That's why Shizu took them in.
Because she wanted to try
and save them.
Back up.
You mean whole nations
are involved in a summoning?
[YUUKI]
Yes.
I suppose that was
this world's choice.
Rather than building armies
to face monsters,
it's far more effective
to just summon
an Otherworlder
of incomparable strength.
So they think, anyway.
You know how powerful Shizu was,
so I'm sure you can understand
their way of thinking.
Yeah, but...
I also understand that Shizu
openly hated this world.
Okay. What'll happen
to these kids?
Five years.
That's how long a Summon
usually lasts.
-So...
-Whoa.
[YUUKI] No one has found a way
to prevent their destruction.
Any children summoned
to this world,
under ten years old,
have all died
within five years.
But hey, just because of that,
those nations were happy
to give us the children
to care for.
[RIMURU]
So, you're saying I can do
whatever I want with these kids
and no one's
gonna complain, right?
Why, do you have
something in mind?
Kind of.
I have to keep my promise
to Shizu.
That much I'm sure of.
Rimuru,
if you can save those kids,
I'd greatly appreciate it.
♪
[RIMURU]
I'll definitely try my best.
Like I always have.
And will continue to do.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
Right!
What's up?
Starting today,
I'm your new teacher!
[RIMURU groans]
[RIMURU]
Wait.
Aren't these kids
supposed to be on death's door?
Shouldn't that excess energy
be incinerating them
or something crazy like that?
[GIRL A]
Whoa, Ken, that was awesome!
[BOY A]
Is that your finishing move?
You totally perfected it.
[GIRL B]
Nah, it wasn't that great.
The teacher even dodged it.
Shut up! I'll get him!
[RIMURU]
What the what?
Did I walk into
the wrong classroom?
These kids are nothing
but hooligans!
He kinda looks like Miss Shizu.
Yeah? You think so?
No way he looks like her.
[RIMURU]
Kenya Misaki, age ten.
Ryota Sekiguchi, age ten.
Gale Gibson, age eleven.
Alice Rondo, age nine.
Chloe Aubert, age ten.
[magic reverberating]
Huh?
That was a weird feeling.
Was it Veldora?
Anyway, since these kids
don't have much time left,
I expected them to be more mild
and a little less monstrous.
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time.
"Shizu's Students."