♪
[gasping]
[gasps]
[guffawing]
The great sorcerer Koenig
is here.
I hope you don't mind
my dropping in.
Leon.
I'll defeat you and claim
my place as the Demon Lord.
It's time
for you to die, pretender!
I see.
While that does sound amusing,
I believe I'll pass.
-Take care of him, Ifrit.
-[gasping]
[LEON]
What's wrong?
[shudders]
[yelling]
You can't just ignore me, Leon,
I will have my fight with you!
How cute, the child
has a death wish.
Very well then.
I'm happy to oblige!
♪
[KOENIG gasps]
[screaming]
[chuckles]
That was quite impressive.
Huh?
[LEON] Tell me, child.
What's your name?
Shizue.
Shizu. Eh?
Hmm.
As of today,
you'll be called Shizu.
[SHIZU]
Shizu?
[barks]
Uh...
[chuckles]
You can eat
all you want, okay?
-[twig snaps]
-Huh?
[gasps]
[PIRINO] Uh, he got separated
from his mother.
Please don't tell
anyone about this.
It'll be our secret.
Do you think I could
help care for him?
[gasps]
Yes. I'd like that.
Look, he's eating it.
[BOTH giggle]
[chuckles]
He's so cute. What's his name?
Monsters don't
typically have names.
[SHIZU] Well, we have to
call him something.
[whimpers]
It sounds like he agrees.
What about "Pizu"?
Pizu.
That's perfect.
Right, Pizu?
[PIZU whimpers]
[gasps]
Look at that.
He just got bigger!
[laughs]
You're such a good boy.
[SHIZU]
Pirino, you know that you can't
take him into the castle, right?
Aw, he'll be okay.
He's really smart.
[SHIZU]
But...
Besides, you've seen
how friendly he is.
I'm sure they'll let him
be my familiar.
[PIZU whimpers]
If you say so.
-[snarling]
-Hey.
Uh, what's wrong with you?
Stop it. Calm down for a second.
-It's okay.
-[snarling continues]
[gasps]
Uh, just be a good boy. Pizu.
[PIRINO gasping]
You're all right.
Everything's fine.
[PIZU snarling]
[PIRINO gasps]
Shizu?
[snarling continues]
A threat.
[PIRINO gasps]
[PIRINO screaming]
[scoffs]
♪
[voice breaking]
What did I just do?
My whole body,
it felt like it was
moving on its own.
And the fire,
it wasn't me.
I couldn't stop!
[crying]
♪
[gasps]
[birds chirping]
[panting]
[gasps]
♪
[footsteps approaching]
[RIMURU] Good morning.
Do you like our little village?
Yes. I love it.
[RIMURU chuckles]
Glad to hear it, Shizu.
You're more than welcome
to stay here.
I appreciate it,
but I really should be going.
[RIMURU]
Why's that?
Because if I do stay here,
I'm afraid I'll bring you
nothing but trouble.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
There's still something
that I need to do.
[RIMURU]
Like what?
I'm on a quest to find the man
who summoned me to this world.
[RIMURU]
What happens when you find him?
♪
[RIMURU]
Okay, then.
Just promise that you'll
come back and visit sometime.
You're always welcome here,
right, Ranga?
Yes, of course.
Well, I'll do my best.
-Thank you. I mean it.
-[RANGA whimpers]
♪
Hey, Shizu. Come back with us.
It'll be fun.
[gasps]
[EREN] Honestly, I'm just
not ready to say goodbye yet.
Eren, you're all
exceptional adventurers.
And I have no doubt that
traveling with the three of you
would probably be entertaining.
So, okay?
Joining with you all
has shown me how good it is
to adventure
with a group of friends.
And I want you to know
I'm truly grateful
that my last journey
was with you guys.
Wait, hold on.
What are you trying to say?
I've been around
for a few decades now.
I may look young,
but I'm not.
Oh. I get it, you were just
making a silly joke, huh?
Sheesh, you shouldn't
scare me like that, Shizu.
Ah. Here they come.
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
We've been standing
out here forever.
Yeah. And why do women take
so long to get ready, anyway?
[gasps]
♪
Why'd you stop?
[groaning]
Is something the matter, miss?
[SHIZU]
No, not again.
-Uh, hey.
-What's happening to her?
[groans sharply]
Something's not right!
[groaning]
[screaming]
♪
What the heck?
What's wrong, Shizu?
[KAVAL gasps]
♪
[RIMURU gasps]
[ALL grunt, scream]
[RIMURU gasping]
[RIMURU]
Whoa! Is everyone all right?
Okay, what the hell?
We're gonna charge
hazard pay for this.
Yeah, well, tell that
to the guild master
next time you see him.
Look up there! It's Shizu!
Wait. Shizue Izawa?
-[EREN gasps]
-You've gotta be kidding me.
Isn't she the Conqueror
of Flames?
-[RIMURU] Huh?
-[EREN] Hold on!
You mean she's
the legendary hero of the guild
from 50 years ago?
They're the same girl?
Impossible.
How?
All the rumors that
I've heard say she's retired.
-[RIMURU] Rigurd. Rigur.
-[BOTH] Hmm?
[RIMURU]
Evacuate the town.
-Are you sure?
-What about you?
[RIMURU]
That's an order.
Of course, as you wish,
Lord Rimuru.
[BOTH panting]
[RIMURU]
Are you there, Ranga?
[RANGA]
Yes, Master. I'm here.
[RIMURU]
I need you to be ready.
[RANGA]
Right!
♪
[grunting]
That thing is Ifrit.
The fire spirit.
Then there's no doubt about it.
That means Shizu...
Is the fabled hero.
She's the Conqueror of Flames.
Ugh. I'm pretty sure we can't
win against that monster.
Yeah, you're right.
I hate to admit it,
but we're as good as dead.
Well, it may have been short,
but at least it was a good life.
♪
[roaring]
-[grunts]
-[ALL scream]
♪
[RIMURU screams, gasps]
[RIMURU] Yo, what gives?
We just built this town, dammit!
[EREN weakly]
That hurt.
[RIMURU] You guys need
to get out of here.
[KAVAL]
We're not going anywhere.
[RIMURU]
Huh?
I don't know what's going on
or why she's out for blood
all of a sudden.
But she's still
a member of our party.
And we won't abandon her.
[RIMURU]
Okay. Just be careful.
They're really good people.
[KAVAL scoffs] I can't believe
we're about to face off
against an actual
legendary hero.
Uh-huh. You never know what life
is gonna throw at you.
[RIMURU]
Let's go.
[RIMURU] Hey, what is it
you want from us?
[RIMURU grunts]
Water blade!
♪
Yeah, I sort of expected that.
-[SALAMANDER screeching]
-[RIMURU gasps]
[gasps]
-[EREN] Icicle lance!
-[RIMURU] Huh?
[screeches]
[RIMURU]
Are you guys doing all right?
We can take care
of these monsters.
Putting our lives on the line
and saving others
is just part
of being adventurers.
What did I tell you
about stealing my lines?
The leader is supposed
to say that.
Well, whatever.
Let's show these lizards
who's boss.
If nothing else, we'll at least
take one of them out.
[RIMURU]
I like your confidence,
but be careful anyway.
Whoa!
[screeching]
♪
Ranga!
[RANGA]
Right!
♪
[RANGA grunts]
[RIMURU]
Here they come.
[RANGA grunts]
[RIMURU] Just concentrate
on evading them.
I'll handle the attacks.
[RANGA]
As you wish!
♪
[RANGA howling]
[RIMURU grunts]
[RIMURU] We can't take out Ifrit
with those salamanders around.
This sucks!
He can vaporize my water blade.
What'll happen
if I just shoot them
with all the water
I have stored in my stomach?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer:
Expulsion of all water
is possible.
If it hits the salamander,
it will cause
an explosion of steam.
Take this action?
[RIMURU]
An explosion, huh?
Will that destroy
the salamanders, though?
[GREAT SAGE]
It is possible.
However, the force of the blast
may destroy
the surrounding area, as well.
[RIMURU]
That seems counter-productive!
[gasps]
Icicle Lance!
♪
[screeching]
[RIMURU] Why does her attack
seem to be doing damage?
[GREAT SAGE] Magic attacks are
more effective against spirits.
[RIMURU]
Light bulb!
-Ranga.
-[RANGA] Yes.
[RIMURU]
Eren, fire that attack at me!
What?
No, I'm not gonna attack you,
that would be crazy.
[RIMURU]
Less talking and more shooting!
[EREN] Okay, prepare for
a face full of ice.
Icicle Lance, go!
Impossible!
He slurped up my ice spear?
[GREAT SAGE]
Notice.
Analysis of Icicle Lance
has been completed.
[RIMURU]
Okay!
♪
Icicle Shotgun!
Oh, yeah!
[screeching]
[RIMURU]
Only one left. Huh?
-[KAVAL] Oh, crap.
-[GIDO] It's gonna blow!
♪
[screams]
[RIMURU]
You guys all right?
That's not good.
[groaning quietly]
[RIMURU] Ranga, take them
and go somewhere safe.
-[RANGA] But, Master--
-[RIMURU] Go!
[RANGA]
Right. As you command.
Be careful.
[RIMURU]
Don't worry.
Ifrit is mine.
[RIMURU]
Now then,
we can finally fight
without holding back.
[RIMURU gasps]
♪
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
Take this! Icicle Shotgun!
It worked!
[gasps]
[roaring]
[RANGA]
Master.
♪
[RIMURU screaming]
[RIMURU]
Why did I just sit there
while he turned up
the heat like that?!
I can't believe
I'm really gonna go out
like a pot of
overcooked pudding!
I just had to get fancy
with the ice moves
when I should have
just demolished this dude
with my Black Lightning!
Figures that right as I was
getting used
to my life as a slime,
I'd go and get
myself incinerated again!
It was a short life.
Or "slife." Whatever.
Weird, but I actually don't feel
like I'm taking much damage.
Why is this taking so long,
is Ifrit some kinda tease?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer:
Due to
Thermal Fluctuation Resistance,
fire attacks are being
automatically nullified
and do not affect you.
[RIMURU]
Ah.
[GREAT SAGE]
Mm-hmm.
[RIMURU]
Why do you sound exasperated?!
Anyway, if I'm immune to
Ifrit's fire attacks, then...
We're playing on easy mode!
It's all good!
No, it's better than good.
It's freaking awesome!
♪
[grunts]
Hmm.
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
Oh, I think I felt an itch.
[grunting]
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
I may have underestimated you,
but not as much as you
underestimated me.
♪
Now it's my turn.
[grunting]
[GREAT SAGE]
Would you like to use
the Unique Skill, Predator?
[RIMURU]
Yes.
[fire crackling]
[gasps]
Shizu!
[water gurgling]
Hmm. Hmm.
[MALE VOICE] You might as well
give up, Ifrit.
♪
[gasps]
[MALE VOICE] It is impossible
to break out of this place.
[gasps sharply]
[MALE VOICE]
You are no match for Rimuru.
He is my sworn friend.
I am the Storm Dragon,
Veldora Tempest.
And it would be
my pleasure to face you.
[VELDORA laughing menacingly]
[laughter continues]
[GREAT SAGE]
Next time, "Inherited Will."