[birds chirping]
Okay, let's take the roll,
shall we?
Kenya Misaki?
Ryota Sekiguchi?
Gale Gibson?
Alice Rondo?
Chloe Aubert?
Hey, come on, kids.
When I call your name
you need to say "here," got it?
Just call it out nice and loud.
All right, I think I've got
a pretty good grasp
on the situation.
So, it's about time
I call in a friend of mine.
[RANGA growling]
-[RIMURU] Kenya Misaki?
-Here!
-[RIMURU] Ryota Sekiguchi?
-Here.
-[RIMURU] Gale Gibson?
-Here!
-[RIMURU] Alice Rondo?
-Uh, here!
-[RIMURU] Chloe Aubert?
-Here.
Good job! Now we're talkin'!
Hey! Calling in that monster dog
to threaten us is dirty!
[groaning]
[RANGA]
My name is Ranga.
Don't forget that, child.
Okay, okay, I get it.
[RIMURU]
Mm-hmm.
Look, you're already
good friends.
How wonderful.
My name is Rimuru,
and starting today I'm your new,
insanely awesome teacher.
Also, I'm probably
not as patient as Shizu.
So keep that in mind.
Oh, my, so quiet!
[growling]
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
Looks like gaining their trust
is gonna be tough.
Not that I can blame them.
They were summoned to this world
and then tossed aside
like garbage.
Right. Pop quiz time.
Doesn't that sound like a blast?
No. Since when
did tests become fun?
I hate them.
[choking]
You can't give us a quiz
on the first day.
Yeah, it's against the rules.
Calm down
before you hurt yourselves.
Look, this is important,
and honestly something
you kids need right now.
Everyone knows
we're gonna kick the bucket.
So why should
we have to study?
It's just a huge waste of time.
Yeah. He's got a point.
And the other teachers always
let us do whatever we want to.
Exactly, we haven't had to study
since we got here.
I just wanna read
my books in peace.
You're the worst!
Bossy jerk-face!
[RIMURU]
Mm-hmm.
You guys have a lot
of fair points.
But relax.
I called it a pop quiz
but it's more like a game.
A game?
You got it.
And it's designed to let you
get your frustrations out.
[KIDS murmur]
[RIMURU] Basically, we're gonna
have one-on-one mock battles.
You've got ten minutes.
If you can take me
out in that time,
I'll declare you the winner.
All you guys have to do
is beat me.
-Is that it?
-[RIMURU] Yup.
-Ten minutes?
-[RIMURU] Uh-huh.
Ha! As long as you don't use
that drool machine,
we won't need ten minutes.
Yeah, using him
would be overkill.
-Ranga, don't interfere, 'kay?
-[RANGA] Right.
Oh, yeah, this will be easy.
All I wanna do is read my book.
Right. Hey, Ryota,
can you be the ref?
[RYOTA]
Uh... Mm-hmm.
Thanks. All right,
who wants to go first?
I'll take you on.
Ahh. They say fortune favors
the bold, eh, Kenya?
[KENYA]
Can we use these weapons?
[RIMURU]
Sure, knock yourself out.
But if you end up losing,
you gotta show me some respect.
Ha! I've never lost a fight
to anyone but Miss Shizu,
so you'd better be ready.
Why don't you
save the smack talk
for when you've beaten me?
[KENYA grunts]
[RIMURU] I'm hoping this fight
will burn off
some of that excess
magicule energy.
If we get rid of it now
maybe it'll save their lives.
Uh... Please begin.
[yells]
Huh?
[grunting]
You!
-You've got this, Ken!
-Don't lose!
I will get you!
[RIMURU] You move pretty fast,
but not fast enough.
[grunts]
[yells]
[RIMURU] Man, are those flames
made out of lame sauce?
The kid's got a lot of energy,
but the weak fire show
is a massive waste of it.
Listen,
instead of throwing fire,
try striking me
with some of that raw energy.
Shut up!
These are the same moves
that Miss Shizu used!
Eat fire!
♪
Stop. The time is up.
[panting]
Well, that's it.
So you'd better get used
to calling me "Teach" now.
Man!
[RIMURU]
Who's next?
[KENYA crying]
You'll regret this!
Guess it's Chloe.
Chloe,
don't push yourself, okay?
Yeah, please be careful.
[RIMURU]
I don't know why,
but this girl
seems familiar somehow.
Like I've seen her before.
-[RYOTA] Begin.
-[RIMURU gasps]
[RIMURU] Is she gonna
chuck a book at me?
That's crazy.
Flow of water,
please ensnare my enemy.
Go, Water Jail.
♪
[RIMURU]
Oh!
She's also a magic user?
This is legit.
I wonder if she's a prodigy.
[CHLOE] So you know,
I can also make blades
come out of the water
that's around you.
Admit defeat and I'll be happy
to withdraw them.
But if you refuse me,
you'll die.
[RIMURU] She's so young
and yet so frightening!
Better hurry up, dude!
Admit defeat, already.
Way to go, Chloe!
-Yeah, awesome job.
-Heck, yeah!
[RIMURU]
Your magic is top-notch.
It's a real shame
that it's not gonna work on me.
♪
-Huh?
-[ALL gasp]
[RIMURU] My Extra Skill
Magic Manipulation
makes escaping
that "Jail" a cinch.
You're pretty good
with that water magic.
You should definitely
keep studying it.
[CHLOE whimpers]
[RIMURU]
She's crying. Sorry, kiddo.
But it's important
that you guys know
how big the power gap is
between us.
[crying]
Don't hold it against me
if I kill you, okay?
[RIMURU] Magic bullets,
and they look strong!
Nope.
That was yummy.
Hey, what gives, man?
You cheated!
Sorry. That's how things are.
As long as you win the fight,
anything goes.
[whimpering]
[RIMURU]
Looks like Ryota's next.
He's seems a little more timid.
Pretty much the exact opposite
of Kenya.
Go, Ryota!
Beat him to a pulp, okay?!
[evil laughter]
[growls]
[yelling]
[RIMURU]
Body Enhancement?
Or is that the Berserker skill?
♪
[yelling]
[grunts]
[snarling]
[RIMURU]
Nice strength enhancement.
If he were fighting anyone else,
he'd probably put up
a decent fight.
But I gotta dock points
for the rabid dog impression
and total lack of control
in battle.
[yelling]
[stones crumbling]
Looks like it's my turn,
so prepare to suffer.
Hmm!
Watch and learn, losers, as I,
the amazing Lady Alice,
enlighten you
on how to win a battle.
Go! Okay, guys, attack.
Take that jerk out!
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Puppetry?
She's a Golem Master?
♪
If she can fight this well
using stuffed animals,
imagine what she could do
with dolls
made from special alloys
as her weapons instead.
Out of the five kids,
her ability might be
the most promising.
But it's kinda annoying.
Maybe I should incinerate
the things.
[GREAT SAGE]
Notice.
The probability that this girl,
Alice Rondo,
would cry is 100 percent.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, maybe not.
Stop. The time is up.
[RANGA panting]
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
Doesn't look like
the magicule count
in their bodies
has been reduced at all.
I wonder,
can I separate them from
the energy using Degenerate?
[GREAT SAGE]
Answer.
The energy has fused
with their souls
and therefore cannot
be separated from them.
[RIMURU]
That sucks.
I don't know how much time
they have left,
so I'll have to look
for another way.
All right, listen up, gang.
[ALL]
Hmm?
As the five of you
have just witnessed,
I am swol.
[ALL]
Huh?
I'm gonna make you a promise.
I will save all of you.
You "promise"?
Yeah. I swear it on this mask.
-[ALL gasp]
-Is that Miss Shizu's?
It sure is.
When Shizu entrusted this to me,
I think she was also
entrusting me with all of you.
Fine, you win.
I've decided to trust you now.
Yeah, I'm gonna trust you, too.
I actually trusted you
from the moment I first met you.
Thanks, traitors.
Ugh, whatever.
Guess I'll trust you, too.
It'll be fine.
And besides, I really do think
he's a person
we can put our faith in.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
Sounds good.
[RIMURU]
Wait.
Didn't Shizu say she was
around the same age
as these kids when she was
summoned to this world?
She said that Demon Lord Leon
made the spirit of Ifrit
possess her.
Could that be it?
-[GALE] Uh, sir?
-[RIMURU gasps]
Are we clear?
I'll save you no matter what.
Shizu's last request was
that I watch over you guys.
I won't abandon you.
[ALL] You're the best!
Thanks, Teach!
[RIMURU]
They called me "Teach."
I'm so happy!
From now on you guys
are my students!
[ALL]
Huh?
[RIMURU]
Uh...
[RANGA panting]
♪
[RIMURU]
Vesta recently taught me
how to use a Warp Portal,
so I used it to go visit Treyni
in the Great Forest of Jura.
[energy humming]
I think that if I can make
superior spirits
inhabit the kids the same way
Ifrit did with Shizu,
we might be able
to control their energy
and save their lives.
[wind rushing]
Lord Rimuru.
What brings you here?
[RIMURU]
What up, Treyni?
Do you know where I can find
some superior spirits?
Let me think.
You could always
try a place called
"The Dwelling of Spirits,"
which is ruled over
by the Queen of Spirits.
[RIMURU]
Sweet!
That sounds exactly like
the kind of place
I'm lookin' for.
Yes.
However...
[RIMURU]
Huh?
[TREYNI]
You see,
there are several entrances
to that domain.
But I'm afraid
that the only one I know of
has long since vanished.
[RIMURU]
What?
The Queen of Spirits who we
once served has passed away.
A rather long time ago,
actually.
And I have no connection
to the current Queen.
I don't know where she resides.
[RIMURU]
Got it.
[TREYNI] I'm sorry that
I couldn't be more help to you.
[RIMURU]
It's okay.
♪
[RIMURU] Don't worry.
I'm gonna keep my promise.
♪
[RIMURU] It's been a month
since I became a teacher.
I've spent that time
trying to figure out
where the superior spirits live,
but I've yet to find
anything useful.
Today, we're having a picnic,
because everyone needs
a break sometimes.
Okay.
Before we have lunch,
I think we should do
a little bit of combat training.
[ALL grunt]
Whoever does their best
will get a reward.
-No way!
-[ALICE screams]
[CHLOE gasps]
A new manga!
[yells]
Oh, man, I can't wait to see
what happens next!
For sure. Things were just
starting to get really good
in the last issue.
Back off, I'm gonna read it
before any of you idiots do!
I like manga.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Not that I know a lot about
Japanese cartoons
and comic books,
but it's still interesting.
Now then, which of you
wants to go first?
Me! I do!
No, me! Me!
-Uh, I'll go.
-Pick me!
[RYOTA]
Me, first.
[GALE]
No way. Let me go first, Teach.
-[overlapping chatter]
-Come on, man, I'm begging ya!
[KENYA exhales]
Aw, man, I can't believe
I lost again today.
Yeah, this isn't fair, Teach,
you're like way stronger.
And aren't you supposed to
take it easy on a lady,
you stupid jerk?!
I need to practice
my magic some more.
No matter what
we can't beat the guy!
[laughing]
Sorry, teenyboppers.
But you're dreaming if you think
you'll ever defeat me.
[KIDS booing]
[laughing]
You did try your best, at least,
so I suppose
I'll let you have this manga.
-[energy humming]
-[RIMURU gasps]
Something wrong?
-[RANGA growling]
-[wind gushing]
♪
That's odd.
The air pressure changed.
[GREAT SAGE]
Notice.
High-density energy
has been detected.
This is due in part
to a Sky Dragon.
A Sky Dragon?
[SKY DRAGON screeching]
-[KENYA groaning]
-[ALICE screaming]
[RIMURU gasps]
Crazy. Is it like a stray?
It's heading
towards the capital.
True that.
I should go do something.
[KENYA]
Huh?
[RIMURU]
I can't just let it run free.
I mean, somebody could
get hurt, right?
Ranga, you stay behind
and protect the kids, okay?
[RANGA] Master, are you sure
you don't want me to go
and give it a good chomping?
Nah, you'd better
leave that guy to me.
Besides, I gotta put on
a good show for these brats.
[RANGA]
Of course.
[KENYA]
Uh, Teach?
I know you're like
mad swol and all that,
but you can't possibly
beat a Sky Dragon.
Yeah, for sure.
If you bite
the bullet in battle,
then who's gonna save us
from dying at a young age?
Chill out, I'm not stupid enough
to take on something
I can't easily beat.
I'll be back in a jiffy.
-Hold up, Teach!
-[ALL] Please, Teach!
Hang on to this for me.
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH grunt]
[overlapping chatter]
♪
Wait, he can fly?
Awesome.
I should probably
disguise myself a bit.
There, that's better.
[ALL screaming]
[SKY DRAGON screeching]
[panting]
♪
[screeching]
[CAPTAIN]
Aim!
Fire!
[arrows clanging]
[energy charging]
[explosions]
[BOTH groaning]
[SKY DRAGON screeching]
[MAN grunts]
[screeching continues]
Damn. Is this the end
of my handsome existence?
Whoa, did you see that?
He completely nullified
its lightning attack.
No way! Is he a Hero?
[SKY DRAGON screeching]
Sheesh, compared to Charybdis,
this is easy.
♪
Hmph.
[gasping]
[RIMURU]
A dinner invite?
Yes.
From a man named Mjolmire.
He's a rather wealthy merchant,
and he would like you
to see the store he runs.
Apparently the children
are invited, too.
[RIMURU]
Okay, but why me?
[YUUKI] Oh, something about
a mysterious warrior
saving his life today.
He defeated a Sky Dragon.
Does that sound familiar?
[RIMURU] Maybe it does,
maybe it doesn't.
So this Mole guy--
[YUUKI]
Mjolmire.
[RIMURU]
Whatevs, is he trustworthy?
[YUUKI]
Well, he's earned
the official
merchant certification
issued by
the Kingdom of Blumund
and the Free Union.
And he might have a side gig
as a loan shark
outside of the public eye.
But I ran a background check
and he is clean.
So I guess he's trustworthy.
[RIMURU]
Hmm.
♪
[KIDS]
Wow!
[KIDS chuckling]
[KIDS]
Mm!
[GALE]
It's delicious!
[ALICE]
It tastes like heaven!
[KIDS chatter]
[MJOLMIRE]
So, how do you like the wine?
Nice. I approve.
I knew that you would.
It's an excellent vintage
that I managed to procure
just recently
via a very special route.
Go on and pour him more.
Uh, hey, are you sure
you don't mind
feeding my students, too?
[MJOLMIRE]
Of course not, it's my pleasure.
I do owe you my life, after all.
Why, whatever do you mean?
Let's just say that I have
a pretty extensive network
for gathering information,
and even with
a different appearance
I know very well
that you were the one
who saved me earlier today.
Nothing can get past me.
A nice dinner is a small price
to pay when I owe you my life,
and I wouldn't dream
of offending my savior.
So, I don't know about you,
but I think this
makes us even.
Wouldn't you agree, sir?
Sure, why not?
[RIMURU]
I guess he's pretty trustworthy
as far as merchants go.
Quick question for you though.
Since you're so knowledgeable,
I assume that you must know
who I am, right?
Correct.
[RIMURU]
Cool, cool.
So why don't you
come to our town?
[gasps]
Wait, are you serious?
Your town?
There's a lot of things
we'd like to start selling,
but we lack the know-how.
If we had your help,
maybe that could change.
And then both parties
would profit.
Oh, uh, I mean,
both parties would benefit.
[laughing]
You've got a deal.
Then it's settled.
[MJOLMIRE] Okay. With this
letter of introduction,
I should be able
to head to your town.
You should come visit again.
I'll cut you some
extra special deals next time.
Yeah, I'm sure you will.
Guard these kids.
May the blessing
of the Queen of Spirits
be upon you.
Miss, is that a magic spell?
No, it's a prayer.
It's something we say
back in my homeland.
It means the Queen of Spirits,
who lives in
the Dwelling of Spirits,
will always watch over you kids.
Hold the phone, lady!
Did you just say
the "Dwelling of Spirits?"
Please tell me
you know where that is.
Uh, yes. I do.
I used to live there.
Well, more like in a village
near there, actually.
[gasps in excitement]
♪
[RIMURU]
In exchange for a generous tip,
the lady told me where to go.
The Ulg Nature Park,
in the northern part
of a frontier nation
called the Republic of Ulgrasia.
This is where
the Dwelling of Spirits is.
Shizu, I swear
that I'm gonna save these kids.
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Conquering the Labyrinth."