[SHIZU]
Mister Slime?
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Thanks so much.
[RIMURU]
Uh...
Ifrit took over.
And I very nearly killed
the people I cared about.
Like last time.
[RIMURU]
Uh...
[SHIZU]
I was wondering...
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Can I tell you something?
You should really
save your strength.
But I want you to know my story.
To know that I lived.
Okay then.
♪
[RIMURU]
So Shizu told me about her life,
though her memory
was a bit fuzzy.
She spoke of Ifrit.
How it possessed her
after she arrived here.
And how she had
killed her own friend.
Everything.
When Pirino died, I stayed.
I had to serve the Demon Lord.
I was his closest aid.
But then, I met someone.
[RIMURU]
Who was it?
[SHIZU]
The Hero.
[RIMURU]
Hero?
[SHIZU]
Yes.
That's right.
There was a battle.
The Demon Lord
abandoned his castle
and left me behind
as the rear guard.
Maybe I stayed there
because it was
the will of Ifrit.
Or maybe it was simply
of my own volition.
I'm still not sure.
♪
[yells]
[shrieks]
♪
[grunting]
[SHIZU]
I can't win.
[gasps]
[RIMURU]
The Hero.
I wonder if she was the same one
who sealed Veldora in that cave.
[SHIZU] I was certain
she would end my life
there on those steps.
But then she surprised me
by speaking instead.
She wanted to know
why I was there
and how I'd managed
to stay alive.
I was a majin.
Yet she still believed
everything I told her.
Then, she said,
"It's all right now."
[crying]
She was able to
unlock my emotions.
After that,
the Hero took me in.
The mask I wear,
it's hers. Or it was.
She said it would boost
my magic resistance
and help suppress Ifrit,
the fire spirit within me.
Allow me.
As we traveled
around together,
I learned about the world,
and she taught me about magic.
Thanks to this mask,
I even learned how to utilize
Ifrit's power,
to some extent anyway.
By helping others and fighting.
[RIMURU] Doing those things
is how you got your nickname
as the Conqueror of Flames,
and rightfully so.
I'm glad I got to
see you in action.
It was awesome!
Being with her
made me very happy.
So I studied
and became her partner.
But then...
[RIMURU]
What?
[SHIZU]
One day, she disappeared
and left me behind.
[RIMURU]
Why?
[SHIZU]
I'm not sure.
I wish I knew,
but I don't.
"I'm certain we'll meet again."
Those were her last words to me.
That day I decided
to become stronger.
I wanted to help people
who were suffering.
♪
So I worked really hard.
For several decades.
Doesn't that sound impressive?
Yeah. It sure does.
People called me a hero
and a champion.
But even though
my body appeared young,
I was still aging.
As I got older, it became
more difficult to control Ifrit.
One wrong step, and I could
release him by mistake.
When I thought about that,
I got scared.
I didn't want to hurt someone,
not again.
Like I had done with Pirino.
♪
Because of that,
I retired and decided
to become an instructor.
[RIMURU]
Sounds like fun.
[SHIZU]
I was a teacher at a school.
[RIMURU]
Whoa! There are schools here?
[SHIZU] Yes,
in the Kingdom of Ingrassia.
I taught kids from other worlds.
[RIMURU]
Kids, huh? That's interesting.
I guess that means Otherworlders
are more common than I thought.
It was actually one of them
who told me about
the video game line you said.
Do you remember what it was?
[BOTH] "Nice to meet you,
I'm not a bad slime, slurp."
[BOTH giggle]
It was a lot of fun.
[laughing]
Hey, teach,
what are we doin' today?
Well, I don't know.
What do you all think
we should do?
Those were peaceful times.
♪
Some of my students left
to pursue their own adventures.
In fact, one of them
is now the Grandmaster.
Grandmaster?
[SHIZU] The person responsible
for overseeing
all the guilds
in every country.
Whoa, kinda sounds
like a big deal.
Yes, it certainly is.
So naturally, I felt like
there was nothing left
I could teach anyone.
But then, as I neared
the end of my life,
it became more difficult
to suppress Ifrit's will.
And I remembered
what I needed to do.
I set out on a new quest.
[RIMURU]
Oh? What for?
[SHIZU] To find the man
who summoned me to this world.
[RIMURU]
Do you want revenge?
[SHIZU]
I don't know, but...
There was something
I needed to find out.
Then I found them.
[inaudible]
They're really good people,
if not a little danger-prone.
[RIMURU]
Yeah, that's true.
[SHIZU]
I had a lot of fun, but now...
Hey, Mister Slime,
will you please
tell me your name?
Huh? I'm Rimuru, remember?
Your real name, silly.
Oh. It's Satoru.
Satoru Mikami.
I'm Shizue.
Shizue Izawa.
[inhales and exhales]
Shizue, you should try
and get some rest.
Satoru.
Can I ask you something?
For a favor?
Of course. Whatever you need.
Could you...
eat me?
[gasps]
Just like you ate my curse.
Right now.
I feel like I'm at peace.
I'm so glad.
I don't love this world, yet...
I can't hate it, either.
Kind of like the man
who summoned me here.
That's why. Why I...
I don't want to be
absorbed by this world.
So please.
This is my last request.
Would you please let me rest
in the one place I'll feel safe?
[RIMURU]
Okay.
♪
What's the man's name?
[SHIZU]
Leon Cromwell.
[RIMURU]
He's a powerful demon lord.
Take care.
What did you wanna
find out from him?
Huh?
I...
I just wanted him
to acknowledge that I,
a human girl,
actually existed.
The kids.
You can still help them.
Maybe they can...
return to their worlds.
[RIMURU] I swear on the name
of Satoru Mikami...
No, on the name,
Rimuru Tempest.
I will make sure
that the Demon Lord,
Leon Cromwell hears
your final wishes.
[weakly]
Thank you.
Shizu...
my destined one,
please rest in peace, within me.
[GREAT SAGE]
Would you like to use
the Unique Skill, "Predator"?
[RIMURU]
Yes.
So that she can dream
happy dreams for eternity
and never have
to wake from them.
♪
Oh, there you both are!
Please don't leave me
behind ever again!
[SHIZU panting]
♪
Huh?
[gasps]
[gasping]
Mother!
[panting]
Mommy!
[voice breaking]
Mommy.
Hey, do you think Shizu's okay?
Don't worry so much.
Besides, Rimuru's
with her, remember?
Yeah, Kaval's right.
Not to mention
you've seen how effective
his healing potions are,
they can fix anything.
[EREN]
True.
[RIGURD]
What a surprise.
Are you all here to visit
our patient as well?
Yeah, is that why
you've come, too?
Yes. Well, and to bring
Miss Shizu
a fresh change of clothes.
Lord Rimuru? Excuse me.
Mm-hmm.
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[RANGA]
Master.
[RIGURD]
That body.
[ALL gasp]
Whoa, hold on!
Are you saying that's Rimuru?
So then, Shizu has passed away?
Hold on, how do we know
for sure you're really Rimuru?
Of course we're sure.
[RANGA]
That's right.
You really think I wouldn't
recognize my own master
just because
his body's changed?
Uh, no, that's not
what we meant at all.
To be honest,
you sort of look like
a younger version of Shizu.
Well, it's me. Watch.
Whoa.
Not gonna lie, I'm impressed.
Does that mean you ate Shizu?
The same way you ate Ifrit?
[RIMURU] I did, but because
it's the only burial
I could give her.
I'm sorry, I should
have consulted you guys
before I did anything.
No. After all, you were just
honoring her last request.
So it's fine.
[RIMURU]
Sorry, Eren.
You must think
I'm a real monster.
Mm-mmm.
But if nothing else,
I wish I could have
at least said goodbye to her.
[RIMURU]
Before she died,
Shizu told me
she had a lot of fun
traveling with you three.
She also mentioned that
you were a bit danger-prone.
-Hmm.
-Uh...
Hey, hold on! Don't blame me.
You're the leader.
-Yeah.
-Huh?
What about you, Gido?
Remember the pit fall?
Hold on, that only happened
because Eren pushed me.
Nuh-uh.
You fell 'cause you're clumsy.
I was too busy...
[RIMURU] Honestly, this behavior
suits them a lot more
than being all sad and stuff.
Don't you think, Shizu?
Actually, it kinda sounds like
you relied on her too much.
[BOTH]
Mm-hmm.
♪
[KAVAL]
We appreciate all your help,
but we should be heading out.
-[RIMURU] Back to your country?
-Yeah.
We gotta report
to the guild master
about what we found here
and about Shizu.
Don't worry, we only have
good things
to say about your village.
We'll tell him
about you, too, Rimuru.
If anything ever comes up,
you can count on us.
[RIMURU] Thank you.
I'll keep that in mind.
♪
[ALL]
Hmm.
Hey, uh, could we possibly
ask you for one more favor?
[RIMURU]
What's up?
Do you think you could
maybe take your
human form again?
[RIMURU]
Huh?
Sure, I guess.
♪
Does this work okay?
[ALL] Shizu, thank you so much
for everything.
[gasps]
And I'll try to be
the kind of leader
you won't have to worry about.
We had some
great times together.
I'll treasure those memories.
[EREN]
Thank you!
You became like
a big sister to me, Shizu.
[crying]
[RIMURU] You know,
I'm actually really glad
that Shizu's last journey was
with these three adventurers.
By the way, what's the deal
with that junk you call gear?
[ALL]
Huh? How mean!
♪
No way!
This stuff's like
my dream armor.
Whoa, look at the quality
of this robe.
And it's light but sturdy,
not to mention gorgeous.
Someone pinch me.
I've never owned
such fine equipment before.
Huh? Whoa! It's even lined
with the fur from a Direwolf.
[RIMURU] They're parting gifts.
Some of our artisans' best work.
[GIDO]
Artisans?
-[RIMURU] Hey.
-[EREN] Huh?
[KAIJIN laughs]
I wouldn't call them
our best work,
they're only prototypes.
So do they fit you all right?
It's all about
craftsmanship, you know?
Mm-hmm.
Say something!
I'll introduce you.
From the right, this is Kaijin,
Garm, Myrd and Dord.
Wait, Kaijin? No way!
[EREN] As in Kaijin,
the world-famous blacksmith?!
[GIDO]
And Garm, Myrd and Dord.
The three renowned
Dwarf brothers?!
Thank you so much!
I'll make it an heirloom.
[EREN]
I'm so happy!
-You just made my life!
-[grunting]
[RIMURU] Wow, I never realized
that Kaijin and his buddies
had such
a prestigious reputation.
They're national treasures.
Or should I say
Dwarven treasures?
After thanking the Dwarves
for so long
that we all got
a little uncomfortable,
the three travelers
went on their way.
I have to admit
they're much more resilient
than I gave 'em credit for.
A woman who lost everything to
the flames when she was a child
ironically managed
to gain the power
of fire in her travels.
She went on to use that ability
to help others who were in need.
But the flames within
gradually consumed her,
until eventually, the day came
where she could
no longer control them.
This woman's name
was Shizue Izawa.
She was a champion,
whose body housed Ifrit.
Harboring the fire spirit
earned her the title,
"Conqueror of Flames."
♪
I won't forget the promise
that I made to Shizu.
But before I can go
and slug Leon Cromwell,
the dumb Demon Lord
who made her cry,
I need to gather
some information.
In the end, I'm a slime
who keeps his promises.
[RIMURU]
There you have it.
That's how the man
who believed he had nothing
but an ordinary
and uneventful life,
a man who was stabbed
on the street and died,
was reincarnated as a slime.
How he went on to inherit
the will of both
the Storm Dragon, Veldora,
and a human woman, Shizue,
and found his purpose.
He was a slime
by the name of Rimuru.
The world he lived in was about
to enter a turbulent new era,
and this small slime would be
at the center of it all.
You know, I still kinda
like this form, too.
[groaning]
[groans sharply]
Hmm.
I think I shall give you
a name and some food.
Who are you?
I am Gelmud.
If you like,
just think of me as your father.
Huh?
Would you prefer to die?
Give me a name.
I'll take that and the food.
Very well,
I shall name you Geld.
Geld, huh?
[GELMUD] One day,
you will take possession
of the Great Forest of Jura,
and become the Orc Disaster.
♪
[groaning]
[GREAT SAGE] Next time,
"Attack of the Ogres."