[GORO] "Yesterday was rainy,
and today is clear.
What will tomorrow be like?"
I'm always trying to determine
what your outlook is.
I can tell what's coming,
be it sudden squalls
or clear blue skies,
by following your gaze.
Your forecasts are always
simple and accurate.
[FUTOSHI]
Hey, guys! They're here!
[ALL gasp, chuckle]
[ZOROME gasps]
Awesome! So which one's mine?
[GROUP chuckles]
I can't believe you still ask
for kiddie stuff like that.
[ICHIGO grunts]
What's it matter to you?
[ZERO TWO]
Presents?
[HIRO]
Yeah. Once every year,
we can ask Papa for
the things we most want.
Then on this one particular day,
we all get them.
Oh! So what's that?
A picture book?
"Picture"? Oh, no.
It's an illustrated guide.
D'you like picture books?
If so, I think we
have some in the study.
[ZOROME]
Okay, listen up!
I'm gonna read
Papa's message now!
Ahem. Uh...
"Boys and girls, your numerous
accomplishments represent
a ray of hope, a harbinger
of peace and prosperity
for mankind. Glory be
to you, noble parasites,
who risk your lives for us."
Ya hear that?
[ALL giggle]
[ZOROME]
He called us "a ray of hope!"
That makes me wanna
work even harder!
♪
[GORO]
Hey, what're you doing.
[ICHIGO]
Shh!
[ZERO TWO]
What's this?
Well, it didn't feel right that
everyone got presents but you.
And so, I wanted
to find something
that I could give to you.
That was left behind by
a girl called Naomi.
Should I not have?
[ZERO TWO giggles]
--Oh, darling! Thank you!
--[HIRO] Whoa, careful!
Who knew getting a
present from someone
could make me so happy?
I'll take good care of it.
[HIRO grunts]
[HIRO]
Your bangs are getting long.
Soon it'll be hard
for you to see.
Think so?
Oh, hey, I decided to ask for
another stuffed toy this year!
How 'bout you?
[HIRO, GORO]
Uh?
[GORO chuckles]
[GORO grunts]
[ICHIGO hums]
[inaudible]
[door clatters]
Hey. There you are.
I was surprised.
By Zero Two, I mean.
I had no idea that she
smiled that way with you.
Uh! What the heck?
You were watching us?
Sorry.
[HIRO]
Isn't that Ichigo's?
Sort of. It's the same type.
But this hairclip here?
I tried and failed to
give her a long time ago.
Huh?
So, remember when I said
I didn't understand that
thing you talked about?
What you called "love"?
Now I'm starting to think
it means the other person
is special to you.
"Special to you"? Yeah, maybe.
When it comes to Ichigo, you've
always been a hero to her.
That sounds pretty special,
doesn't it?
Where's all this coming from?
Well, I think she probably
feels the same way for you,
as you do for Zero Two.
Whaddaya mean?
Y'know, it's like, she wants
to know you better.
And uh, do that
"kiss" thing with you.
[gasps]
Ha. Come on. You're tellin'
me you really haven't noticed?
What? But that's--! Whoa, wait.
Doesn't that mean you...?
[GORO]
I know everything.
I know what would
make her laugh,
and what would make
her cry. Everything.
But they wouldn't work
for me. You, though?
You could make them work.
Goro. You're bein'
kinda weird today.
[GORO]
Yeah, I know it's weird.
It's just, watching you lately,
made my own feelings
clear to me.
It helped me realize...
I love Ichigo.
[gasps]
[GORO yawns] Feels good
to get that off my chest.
Well, time for bed.
[HIRO]
Hold on!
[GORO]
You know what, though?
I'm plenty happy with the
way things are right now.
You ready?
Oh, one second.
[ICHIGO]
Ready.
[IKUNO]
Good night.
[HACHI] We've detected a
Guttenberg-class klaxosaur
at a distance of
approximately 2,000.
While it's moving slowly,
based on its course,
we predict that it will make
contact with the plantation.
We must avoid a repeat of the
previous attack at all costs.
[ALL]
Right!
Now then. Since the target's
farther away this time,
your units have been loaded
with more fuel than usual.
So make a note of that.
[KOKORO] Look, you guys.
There's a huge thundercloud.
[IKUNO]
That doesn't seem right.
What is that?
KLAXOSAUR roars]
[HACHI]
Target sighted.
[MIKU]
It's kinda gross!
[HACHI]
All units, prepare for combat.
Roger that!
[ZOROME, MIKU]
Argentea, going in!
[MIKU shouts]
[MIKU gasps]
[MIKU grunts]
[MIKU shouts]
What the--?
[ICHIGO]
Bombs?
[KLAXOSAUR roars]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
This is... not good.
[ZOROME]
Damn it.
[ZOROME gasps] Hey, look,
the core's right there!
[ZOROME chuckles]
[ZOROME]
You're mine!
Idiot! Don't!
[MIKU]
That's hard!
[MIKU grunts, shouts]
[ZOROME]
What's up with this thing?
[MIKU]
We can't break free!
Oh, no!
--[ICHIGO grunts]
--[MIKU gasps]
[ICHIGO grunts]
[MITSURU]
It's doing something!
[HIRO]
Ichigo! Goro!
[ICHIGO]
I can't move!
[GORO]
Everyone, get away!
[ALARMS blaring]
[GORO grunts]
[GORO sighs]
[HIRO]
Ichigo! Goro!
[ICHIGO]
I can't move!
[GORO]
Everyone, get away!
[GORO grunts]
[HIRO]
Goro.
[GORO]
Hiro?
[HIRO] Thank goodness.
I finally got through.
[GORO]
How's Ichigo?
[HIRO]
She's fine.
She got knocked
out by the ejection,
but there were no
serious injuries.
She's being treated along
with Zorome and Miku.
Oh, good. That's a relief.
Hey, Hiro? Could you contact
the transport team for me?
I can't exactly operate
this thing alone.
[HIRO]
Goro. Try to keep calm, okay?
[GORO gasps]
[HIRO] Right now you're
in the klaxosaur.
[GORO gasps]
What does that mean?
We didn't eliminate the thing?
[HIRO] As it exploded,
it swallowed Delphinium.
Not long after that,
we were ordered to retreat.
So for the moment, we're all
back at the plantation.
That's how it happened, huh?
[FUTOSHI] But don't worry, we're
gonna get you out of there!
We just need to figure out how!
Right. I'll try to come up
with something on my end.
[HIRO]
Goro...
I'm sorry that we had
to leave you behind.
[GORO]
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, I'm wasting power here,
so I'm gonna switch to
safe mode for a bit.
[HIRO]
All right. We'll be in touch.
Without a pistil
aboard the FRANXX,
he can't use its
magma energy.
You mean...
No need to worry.
After all, the FRANXX's life
support systems run off
of backup power.
[ZERO TWO] Which... means if
it runs out, he'll die.
[ALL gasp]
Well, as things stand now,
this plantation,
along with all of us,
will soon be going kaboom.
[MIKU]
Hang on!
[IKUNO gasps]
Ichigo?
You should still be in bed!
I need answers. What's this
about Goro getting swallowed up?
Like I already told you,
he was trying to save us and...
"And"? Why aren't we
rescuing him yet?
How could you turn tail?
This very second, he's trapped
inside that klaxosaur!
That fool. Why did he
cut me loose like that?
Without me, he knows
that he's helpless!
Ugh. So annoying. C'mon, girl.
How have you not realized
that Goro is always
--looking out for you?
--[ICHIGO] What?
Like that time when
Hiro almost died.
You immediately broke down,
and who was it that got
you back on your feet?
What makes you think
you have the right
to run your mouth at me?
You're always like,
"I'm the leader."
But when things go wrong, you
lose it and take it out on us.
Do you get what I'm saying?
Goro must be miserable
with you as a partner!
[ICHIGO grunts]
[door hisses]
All right, girls, that's enough.
I'm glad to see you
children are okay.
Good, you're all here.
We've analyzed the samples
stuck on your units.
The results show this klaxosaur
can vaporize its bodily fluids
to expand and explode.
Wait. You mean what
Goro's stuck in
is essentially its fuel source?
[HIRO gasps]
Just relax. Fortunately,
we've confirmed several details
about this creature.
Such as the part Delphinium
jumped into being harmless
to FRANXX.
All right! Then the first order
of business is rescuing Goro!
I do owe him one, after all.
The top priority, is keeping
the target from the plantation.
[KIDS gasp]
[HACHI] Estimated time of
contact is approximately
one hour from now.
We'll set up a last
line of defense,
and eliminate the klaxosaur
before it crosses that line.
But, sir, what if we can't
eliminate it by then?
In that case, the planation
will open fire, as well.
The target will defend
itself by detonating its
internal fuel several times.
However, if we launch
enough strikes,
there's a chance one
will eventually finish it.
[ALL gasp]
Are you telling us you
would leave Goro to die?
In the worst-case
scenario, absolutely.
No way.
[HACHI]
You have your orders.
The operation begins
in 15 minutes.
All hands, prepare to sortie.
[ALL gasp]
[ICHIGO] Sir. Please allow me to
speak to Goro before we start.
[GORO]
Is that water?
How long ago did Hiro radio?
Thirty minutes?
[GORO] There's only
one thing I can do now.
[ICHIGO]
Goro.
Ichigo? You're up.
Thank goodness.
[ICHIGO]
You idiot!
What were you thinking, getting
yourself swallowed whole?
Why do you always put
yourself second like this?
How are you going to get
out of there without me?
You've always been
like this, too!
Making selfish decisions.
And every time, it ends up
with you coming back hurt!
Why don't you ever just
lean on me a little?
I'll save you. No matter what,
I'll save you.
So wait for me!
Ichigo.
[gasps] Whoa, hold on.
Are you crying?
[ICHIGO]
Shut up.
It's all right, Ichigo. I came
up with a really good plan.
I'm gonna kill this thing.
Then I'm coming back home
to you, so don't worry about me.
How are you gonna kill
it when you can't move?
[GORO] I gotta go.
I can't waste more power.
No, Goro!
Hey. I've got this,
even by myself.
[gasps]
[breathes heavily]
[ICHIGO]
Please, let me rescue Goro!
If I know him, he's thinking
of doing something stupid!
He's just trying to
act tough! I can tell!
[HIRO]
She's right! Please, let us go!
[NANA] And how exactly do
you intend to rescue him?
Well, I suppose.
[ZERO TWO]
There was one spot.
On top of the klaxosaur is an
exhaust hole of some sort.
A person could probably slip
in there if they really tried.
[gasps]
[HACHI] Genista and
Chlorophytum are standing by
as the last line of defense.
If it looks like the target is
going to cross that point...
Right. I understand.
[HIRO] You'll have to cross an
area of highly pressurized
vapor fuel to get
to Delphinium.
There's no guarantee you'll
be safe, even in your suit.
[ICHIGO] Yeah, I know.
But there's a chance.
Isn't that right?
[ZERO TWO] We can't be sure.
If it were me, I wouldn't do it.
[HIRO]
Hey! Zero Two!
[ICHIGO] Well, I will.
And Zero Two? I believe in you!
[ZERO TWO]
I can't say I dislike that.
[ZOROME]
Let's go! Upsy-daisy!
[HIRO] Ichigo! Get Goro.
Bring him back.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[MIKU]
Hurry up!
[ICHIGO]
Just you wait, Goro!
[GORO breathes heavily]
[BOY A] Why does that guy
keep picking fights with us?
[GORO]
Sick of the communal lifestyle,
I thought I'd get to be alone...
...if I could make
everybody else hate me.
[ICHIGO] Hey, you shouldn't
pick so many fights
when you're so weak.
Stay out of it!
[GORO grunts]
C'mon, bring it, tough guy.
[ICHIGO]
Told ya so.
I've got this,
even by myself.
[ICHIGO]
Here.
[GORO grunts]
[BOYS grunt]
Just so we're clear,
I never asked for your help.
[ICHIGO]
Yeah, but we won.
Maybe we can't win alone,
but we can when we're together.
[GORO gasps]
[GORO] Yeah. Ever since then,
I've loved Ichigo.
And always right
beside her... was Hiro.
[GORO]
But I was okay with that.
Because Hiro was special
to me, too. In his own way.
[breathes heavily]
C'mon, you two,
you better not die.
[MIKU] There's Genista
and Chlorophytum!
[IKUNO] We're in trouble
if it gets past us.
[KOKORO] It'll be fine.
Just believe in Ichigo.
[GORO] I used to think I didn't
mind if my feelings never got
through to her. But, if there's
one thing I regret...
[breathes heavily]
[GORO] That's more than
enough to self-destruct.
And there's the
backup fuel, too.
[chuckles] This is gonna
be one hell of a present.
I just wish I coulda told her.
[ICHIGO grunts]
Ichigo?
[ICHIGO coughs]
[ICHIGO]
Wow. The air's so thin.
[GORO]
Why'd you come?
I said I'd save you
no matter what, right?
[GORO grunts] And I said
not to worry about me.
Yeah, well, you're an idiot,
so I knew you would try to
fix everything by yourself.
You're so headstrong,
even though you're weak.
Even though you can't
do anything without me.
That doesn't mean
you had to come here.
That's where you're wrong.
"Maybe we can't win alone,
but we can together," right?
[gasps]
[GORO]
You were willing to cry over me.
I thought I could be
satisfied just knowing that...
...until a moment ago.
But now, seeing your face...
as you smile at me...
...is making me happier than
anything ever has before.
What are you doing?
Quit being weird.
Let's get out of here already.
[GORO gasps]
Let's do this, Ichigo!
[ICHIGO]
Roger!
[HIRO]
They're out!
[ZOROME]
Aw, yeah!
[GORO] Guys, get the
hell away from here!
[MIKU]
Huh?
[GORO]
Hurry!
There. All done.
Thank you.
[GORO gasps]
Hey, wait. Where's your clip?
[ICHIGO gasps]
Huh? Oh, no. Did I lose it?
It's okay.
[ICHIGO]
Oh. You had it the whole time.
Yes, but no.
This is something I wanted
to give you a long time ago,
but never could.
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
Y'know what? I think
I love you, Ichigo.
Huh?!
[GORO chuckles] There's no
need to get so flustered.
I just felt like
I had to tell you.
[ICHIGO exhales]
Because... I don't wanna
look back and wish I had.
I want no regrets, ever again.
Now that you say that,
there's something I feel I
have to tell you, as well.
[GORO gasps]
Thank you for being
my partner, Goro.
[GORO gasps]
[ICHIGO]
But, um,
I... don't know how to
respond to the love thing.
Sorry. I wasn't trying
to put you on the spot.
And I'm not expecting
an answer or anything.
[ICHIGO gasps]
But could I stay
like this for a bit?
[ICHIGO]
Mm-hm.
Tears one minute,
smiles the next.
Man, I don't get
you at all today.
[GORO]
What's the outlook for tomorrow?
Right now, you're impossible
to forecast.
♪