[PAPA] Lately, we have
observed a sharp increase
in klaxosaur activity.
Most distressing is
that the large ones
are now appearing everywhere,
which is unprecedented.
[MALE SAGE B] For now,
the Nines are dealing with them.
However, they still have
other tasks to complete.
[MALE SAGE C] How long do we
plan on letting Strelizia
goof off?
Now that we've ascertained
the special specimen's aptitude,
we have no reason to
keep it there any longer.
[FEMALE SAGE A]
Agreed.
It's unwise to let her mix
with tainted stamens
any more than she already has.
[MALE SAGE A] But if we
are going to recall her,
then we'll have to
ready a new stamen.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
That won't be a problem.
There are plenty of parasites
eager for the chance
to partner with her.
♪
Demon. She's a demon!
You'd have to be insane to ride
with her. She'll kill you!
[FUTOSHI sighs]
[ICHIGO]
How is he?
He hasn't touched
any of his food.
Maybe I should eat it,
so it doesn't go to waste.
He's been like this
since we got back.
[ZOROME, KOKORO gasp]
[HIRO] Mitsuru. What happened
with Zero Two?
[MITSURU]
What... happened?
That "girl." She tried to
devour everything I have.
My blood. My flesh.
My soul. All of it.
Everything was normal at first,
but then, after a point,
she was out to kill me!
Mitsu--
The worst part was her smile.
She smiled the whole time!
[HIRO gasps]
Mitsuru!
Calm down, man!
[MITSURU] Ride with her again,
and it'll happen to you.
You'll end up no
different than me!
You're outta your mind if you
think you're the exception!
No one is safe
with that monster!
[FUTOSHI]
Mitsuru, stop!
[FUTOSHI] Lie back and
try to get some rest.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
[FUTOSHI]
Got it!
There!
[ZOROME]
Too easy!
[ICHIGO] Do you still
want to ride with her?
[ZOROME] You gotta cut
down on the snacks...
No matter how hard I try.
I can't bring
myself to trust her.
And especially not after
what happened to Mitsuru.
--[ZOROME laughs]
--[FUTOSHI] You jerk!
--Can't get me!
--Get back here!
[ICHIGO] If everything about the
partner killing rumor is true,
Hiro, you'll die after riding
with her two more times.
Even so. If I ride with her,
I finally get the chance to be
of some use in this world.
[ICHIGO grunts]
So, you've made up your mind.
Fine. I won't try
to stop you again.
Ichigo...
[ICHIGO] As leader, I have
to steel myself to emotion.
[door rattles]
Steel yourself, huh?
[HACHI] Yes, klaxosaurs
must be eliminated,
but despite that, it doesn't
mean we give you free reign
in your methods.
They were Conrad-class.
You didn't need to use that
much power against them.
But because you did, we nearly
lost one of our parasites.
Are you listening?
I wanna leave this place.
I feel like I'm suffocating.
Excuse me?
As long as I have my darling,
I don't care what happens.
After all, those other
kids'll die soon anyway.
Zero Two!
Even if those children are from
a differnet unit than you,
they are still your
fellow FRANXX pilots.
My fellow? Seriously?
Those weaklings are
only a nuisance,
no matter how many
of them there are.
They're an irregular squad, yes.
But each one is a
parasite carefully chosen
for their high aptitude.
[ZERO TWO]
Yeah.... Sure they were.
You doubt them...
because you are special.
Hold on. Are you talking
about how I'm not human?
I'm talking about your
talents and nothing else.
That said, it's
unlikely they'll let
Zero-One-Six pilot Strelizia.
And why is that?
We received new orders
from HQ earlier.
They want you back fighting
on the front lines.
[ICHIGO] If everything about the
partner killing rumor is true,
Hiro, you'll die after riding
with her two more times.
[MITSURU] But then, after a
point, she was out to kill me!
The worst part was her smile.
She smiled the whole time.
[grunts]
[ZOROME] Hiro's training
by himself again?
Leave him alone and
he'll run forever.
He's surprisingly
hardworking, isn't he?
Anyone else would've
given up by now.
Wait a sec.
Does he still want to ride with
that girl after what's happened?
[GORO] Well, if she's the
only one he connects with,
riding with her's the
only way he can stay here.
But on the flip side,
if Zero Two gets sent away,
then doesn't that mean
Hiro has to leave as well?
[GORO]
I would assume so.
[KOKORO]
As awful as it sounds,
maybe Hiro would be better
off going with Zero Two.
I'd hate for him to
be alone forever.
I'm sorry, but I think
you forgot a small detail.
That girl has klaxosaur blood
running through her veins!
She isn't human. You want Hiro
to go through what Mitsuru did?
He knows all the risks and
he doesn't care. That's that.
Ichigo?
[ICHIGO] He's not the only
one staring death in the face.
If things don't change soon,
we could all wind up
dead at any moment.
[ICHIGO] If we can't defeat the
klaxosaurs without Strelizia,
then that's it.
We won't survive.
We can't afford to
screw up. Not anymore.
It's not like you
didn't screw up, too.
[ICHIGO] You're right.
And it won't happen again.
But I need you to help
ensure it doesn't!
We're a team! Let's act like it!
A team. Ichigo's right.
Eh! We didn't need you
to spell that out.
Good speech. A true leader.
Yeah. It's about time we
show Papa and the rest
what we're really capable of!
[KOKORO]
Mm-hm!
[FUTOSHI]
If we do well,
we'll be on the fast
track to the top!
[ICHIGO]
We need you, too.
Okay? I'm sure Mitsuru knows
he can't mess up either.
So, be there for him,
as his partner.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
'Kay.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
To prepare for the kissing
with Plantation 26,
Plantation 13 will now
switch to mobile set up.
I repeat.
To prepare for the kissing
with Plantation 26,
Plantation 13 will now
switch to mobile set up.
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO]
Why did I just hide from her?
Two more times.
Should I?
[ZERO TWO]
There you are.
[HIRO gasps]
[gasps] What're you
doing in here?
[gasps]
You're... really close.
Darling... Run away with me.
Then we can forget all about
those other weaklings.
As long as we're together,
nothing else matters.
You're the only one who
can be my partner.
[HIRO gulps]
Or am I wrong? Are you
just like everone else?
Do you think I'm a monster?
[gasps]
[alarm blaring]
Oh, no!
[SOLDIER A]
Worm-type klaxosaur detected.
Heading toward Plantation 13.
Must've reacted to
the energy emitted
from the mobile
kissing set-up.
[MITSURU grunts]
Shit. I can do this. I can!
[IKUNO]
Want some help?
[MITSURU grunts]
I can handle it.
This is nothing.
[IKUNO]
Hold on to me.
I don't need your help.
[IKUNO grunts]
You're so stubborn.
[HACHI] We haven't
identified its class yet.
And while we've only
confirmed this one so far,
there may be more
in hiding, so be careful!
[ALL]
Roger that!
Commence connecting!
I hope for both of our sakes
that you can do this.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine this time.
[grunts]
[ICHIGO]
We'll stop it here!
[HIRO]
That the only one?
As of now, yes. Don't think
putting on your suits
means we'll deploy Strelizia.
[ZERO TWO scoffs]
We didn't say that,
so you're thinking it.
[ICHIGO grunts]
[KOKORO gasp]
[MIKU grunts]
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
On three! One... Two...
Is it dead?
[GORO] No, I doubt it. I don't
think anyone got its core.
[MIKU]
Well, if we missed its core,
then we better get back to work.
You can't kill a klaxosaur--
[MIKU yelps]
[IKUNO]
There's another one?!
[KOKORO]
We're coming!
[KOKORO gasps]
[IKUNO grunts]
[MIKU grunts]
[ICHIGO grunting]
Dammit... Hold on!
[ALL shout]
[KOKORO]
From below?
[ALL scream]
Just saying. This wouldn't
be happening if we were
out there right now.
Out of the question.
Tsh. Killjoy.
By the way, that transport that
just landed, who's in it?
[door hisses]
[SOLDIER B]
Code Zero-Zero-Two.
You're coming with us.
[NANA] Your escorts. And I'd
obey them, if I were you.
Zero Two, as I said before,
you're going back
to the front lines.
By yourself, of course.
[HIRO]
Wait. I don't understand, why--
[SOLDIER B]
Let's go!
It's easier to leave while that
klaxosaur is preoccupied.
Don't touch me!
[SOLDIER B grunts]
[SOLDIER C gasps]
[SOLDIER D]
Freeze!
What's this about, Zero Two?
[ZERO TWO] Darling.
Looks like our time is up.
[gasps]
Although I wish it wasn't.
I honestly believed things could
work out between the two of us.
I truly wanted to be with you.
But now, this is goodbye.
[HIRO grunts]
But... why?
Bye, Darling.
[SOLDIER D]
Move.
[NANA] Hiro... It was a
direct order from Papa.
[HIRO]
Are the rumors about her true?
That she's a "partner killer"?
It's complex.
Zero Two is a unique
individual that must be kept
on the front lines of this
battle. She's a special pistil.
But with that comes a
great toll for any stamen
who is assigned to
be her partner.
Remember. She's not like you,
or the others in your squad.
[HIRO]
Are you saying she isn't human?
[NANA] That's exactly
what I'm saying, Hiro.
[HIRO]
Is that really how it is?
Also. It's nice that you weren't
frightened by my horns at all.
Are you just like everyone else?
Do you think I'm a monster?
I truly wanted
to be with you.
Bye, Darling.
[HIRO]
No. She is just like us.
[NANA gasps]
What're you doing? Hiro!
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO]
Huh?
[SOLDIER D]
What wrong?
It's nothing.
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[gasps]
[HIRO]
Don't go! Damn it. Stop!
[grunts] Listen to me!
Please, wait!
I was afraid to ride
with you, I admit it!
Honestly, I'm still
kind of afraid.
But that fear has nothing
to do with the fact
that you aren't human.
It's because I lack resolve!
When we met by that lake,
I couldn't take my
eyes off of you.
You looked so strong.
So confident.
And when you were hurt, you
jumped right back in the fight,
and I found that beautiful.
I'd been moping around.
But during that time I
got to spend with you,
I felt like I could fly!
And you made me realize
that I never really cared about
riding in a FRANXX at all.
What mattered was
riding in one with you!
So please, don't
leave me! Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
[SOLDIER D]
Hey, keep moving.
[ZERO TWO]
How can I leave after that?
[SOLDIERS gasp, grunt]
[gasps]
[HIRO gasps]
Zero Two.
You're the first person tell
me something so embarrassing.
It's my first, too.
Do you wanna ride now?
I do.
Lemme hear you say it.
[gasps]
Okay. I wanna ride in
Strelizia with you again!
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
Now that's what I
expect from my darling!
[ZERO TWO]
Fast as you can!
[SOLDIER E] Hey! Those two
got through the gates!
[SOLDIERS]
Huh?
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO, SOLDIER G grunting]
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[SOLDIER F]
Hold it!
You vacate that
FRANXX right now!
I can't. I'm going
out with my darling!
You don't have permission--
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Something wrong, Darling?
What if I can't pilot?
What'll happen?
You can. We can do this!
Well, are you ready?
[HIRO inhales]
Yeah.
[HIRO]
It'll be all right.
If I'm with Zero Two,
I can do this!
[ZERO TWO]
Now, darling, let's fly!
I did it. Ha, ha!
I'm doing it! I'm piloting!
[ZERO TWO] That's right!
This is what you're capable of!
This feeling, though, it's like
I'm deep inside of you.
I can't tell where I end and
you begin. And yet, I love it!
[ZERO TWO]
I'm feeling it, too.
[ZERO TWO giggles] We're a
perfect match for each other.
And the real fun
is still to come!
--[KLAXOSAUR A roars]
--[ICHIGO] Shit!
[gasps]
[KLAXOSAUR A roars]
[ICHIGO]
Strelizia?
[MIKU yelps, grunts]
[GORO]
Whoa, is that Hiro?
[FUTOSHI]
Unreal!
[HIRO]
Let me handle this!
[ICHIGO] No! We can't afford
to rely on Strelizia this time!
Ichigo! I'm part of the team!
[MITSURU grumbles]
[ICHIGO] All right then, Hiro.
You take that one.
Meanwhile, we'll focus
on this one here.
[ZERO TWO]
That didn't feel right.
Gotta find its core.
[HIRO grunts]
[KLAXOSAUR A roars]
[ZERO TWO]
No you don't!
[ZERO TWO shouts]
[ICHIGO gasps]
[HIRO]
What the--?
[ZOROME] No way!
It's all one klaxosaur?
[FUTOSHI] Finding the core
in something this long
is not gonna be easy!
[GORO] It's still the
only way to kill it!
[MIKU shouts]
[IKUNO, ICHIGO grunt]
[MIKU] We can't find it if
it won't stop squirming!
[ICHIGO]
I'm on it!
[ICHIGO shouts]
[ICHIGO]
Come on!
[ALL]
Mm. Right!
[MIKU shouts]
[KOKORO shouts]
Okay, guys. Now that
we got it pinned down,
what're we gonna do with it?
[ICHIGO grunts]
[IKUNO grunts]
[KLAXOSAUR A ROARS]
[MITSURU]
Not on my watch!
[ICHIGO grunts]
Hiro! We need you!
Whaddaya think? We got this?
[ZERO TWO]
Easily.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro!
--[ZERO TWO] Hmph!
--[ICHIGO gasps]
[ZERO TWO, HIRO yell]
[panting]
[HACHI] Target neutralized.
All units, return to base.
[NANA] I can't believe she
ignored Papa's orders.
Was she planning on
this all along?
[computer beeps]
Perhaps. But her stunt
today changes everything.
The numbers conclusively show
Zero-One-Six's
compatibility with her.
How will Papa and
the others react?
[HIRO] I'd always dreamed of
the day I could take flight
to the skies above.
And for a while,
I had given up on that
dream ever coming true.
But now?
I may have finally found a
pair of wings to call my own.
And though they may be
double-edged ones
that will slowly destroy me,
I will still get to fly with
them again. One more time.
♪