[HIRO] This is a beast
princess's love story.
One day she met a human prince,
and wished to
become one with him.
"I want to live as a human.
I want to be united with him".
The witch replied like so,
"I can help you, if you
offer me your wings.
But keep this is mind.
No matter how you disguise
yourself, you are a beast,
and you will consume the
prince's life one day."
The princess ripped
off her wings,
and was assaulted by
pain far more intense
than she had ever felt.
She could never fly again.
Even so, she smiled happily,
with tears of joy
streaming down her face.
"I'm human! I'm human!
I'm the same as him now"
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
♪
[MALE SAGE A] Our parasite
reserves have dwindled
to a mere 60&amp;
after the last battle.
[MALE SAGE C]
Don't you think we went too far
by detonating
the plantations?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
The ends justify the means.
Humanity now has control
of the Gran Crevasse.
Hringhorni's construction has
entered the final phase as well.
[PAPA]
The time has come.
I've already sent two
messengers to you-know-where.
This will likely be our
final warning to them.
There is no need for two keys.
Now, Klaxosaur Princess,
what will you choose?
[FUTOSHI] That day, in the
Battle of the Gran Crevasse,
our plantation
was left in ruins.
However, we're still living
here, inside Mistilteinn.
"We are to stand by and
wait for our next mission".
One month has already
passed since we were
given those orders.
[gasps] It's Papa!
[FUTOSHI] We children have
always lived by ourselves,
but some things have changed.
The damage to the plantation
has affected the water
supply system, and we've
also had to restrict
our electricity usage.
And to top it all off,
our mysterious caretakers
are gone now.
One, two!
[chuckles]
--[banging]
--[KOKORO gasps]
Man talk about making a racket.
Looks like she's on
messenger duty this week.
Sure does.
[FUTOSHI] The only thing we were
told was that food supplies
would be delivered to us
once a week. That was all.
We're spending our days
completely in the
dark about things.
It's the same here.
The water's foul.
True. But it might
still be drinkable.
At least, maybe if we filter it.
That said, there's no
telling how much longer
we'll be able to keep this up.
The water supply to this
area could stop at any time.
Yeah, you're not wrong.
[banging]
Found you. Let's go, you two,
it's time to make breakfast!
Take care of this, darling.
You can pour those.
--[HIRO] Doing okay?
--[ZERO TWO] Yep!
[ZOROME] I'm starving! Or was.
We're having this again?
What else can we do?
If you don't wanna eat it,
no one's going to force you to.
[ZOROME] Hey, I never
said I wouldn't eat it!
[IKUNO]
Sorry I'm late. Let me help.
No. We've got it.
Anyway, has your
fever gone down?
At this point, I think
I'm just used to it.
[ALL gasp]
[ZERO TWO] Thirty-six point
seven degrees. Normal.
But don't push yourself, okay?
[IKUNO] Uh. I won't.
Thanks, Zero Two.
[ALL]
May Papa never thirst.
May Papa's heart be filled
with peace for all eternity.
And now let us eat.
The morning laundry's
all finished.
Carrying the rations
is taken care of.
Right now we've got 30
minutes for breakfast.
After that is...
You're awfully meticulous.
It's not like anybody's
gonna complain
if you get a little
bit off schedule.
We agreed to these rules.
There'll be no exceptions.
We're the only ones here,
so we gotta obey them.
Wow, somebody certainly turned
over a new leaf. I'm impressed.
It's like your wild side's
completely gone now.
Exactly. That's why I
wanna do things right.
[MIKU]
Oh? Really?
[ZERO TWO]
Yes, really!
What's wrong, Futoshi?
Are you not feeling well?
[FUTOSHI]
Huh? No, I'm fine.
It's just, you know,
I'm on a diet!
You and diet in the
same sentence?
I don't think you
can hack it, big guy.
[FUTOSHI]
Say what?!
[ZOROME]
It'd be a waste of time!
[FUTOSHI]
We don't know--!
[FRANXX]
You haven't made contact?
[HACHI]
That's right.
[FRANXX] Good. If you
intervene with the children,
this whole project
will be ruined.
Doctor. I fail to
understand this.
At this rate, all of our efforts
will have been in vain.
Those kids went to hell
and came back alive.
I'm sure they will
continue to be assets
to Papa and the others.
Even if we keep the test going--
[FRANXX]
Always so inflexible.
You've been down this
road too, you know.
[NANA gasps]
[FRANXX]
Hachi. Keep it up.
[NANA]
Doctor!
What is with him? Good grief.
[GORO]
It's been one whole month.
How much longer will we
have to stand by here?
[HIRO] Anxious to get
back in the FRANXX?
[GORO] You know, we've
been fighting in battles
where we could die at any time.
Yet, not being in combat
makes us... all fidgety.
I'm surprised though. Out of
all of us, I thought you
were the one most obsessed
with piloting the FRANXX.
[KOKORO]
You want me to cut your hair?
Just where is this coming from?
Uh! I mean. I don't mind at all!
I'd love to if you're
okay with it!
Honestly, what was
I even hoping for?
[KOKORO]
Huh?
[MITSURU]
Did I want him to apologize?
Or was I searching for a
reason to forgive him?
[MITSURU]
I got it all mixed up.
Both the promise we'd made,
and how he'd forgotten about it.
He had done nothing wrong.
Maybe I was using
my grudge against him
just so that I could carve
out a niche for myself.
Now, without it, I have nothing.
[KOKORO]
Mitsuru, look up.
[MITSURU]
Huh?
[chuckles]
Hey. What's so funny?
Uh. Oh, no. Do I look weird?
[KOKORO]
Mm-mm. You look very handsome.
[MITSURU]
Huh?
If you understand all that,
then it means you
can start over again.
Even after the
misunderstandings,
the promise the two of
you made is still real.
That's what I believe, anyway.
Thanks, Kokoro.
That means a lot.
You know, it's funny.
Hearing you say that makes me
feel like I can do anything.
[gasps]
You're a very kind person,
and talented with your hands.
[MITSURU gasps]
[gasps] Oh, no, what have I...?
I'm... I'm so sorry!
[door clatters]
[HIRO] Goro's temperature
also started rising last week.
It must be the Child Fever.
Since that battle,
everything's been different.
Our environment's changed,
our lifestyle.
What are you doing?
Oh. Those are Sakura buds.
"Sakura"? What do the
flowers look like?
When they bloom?
Uh, let me think.
Well. They're a
very pretty color.
The same as your hair, actually.
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
I can't wait to see them!
[HIRO] How do you feel
about our lives right now?
[ZERO TWO]
I'm having fun.
[HIRO]
You don't think it's a pain?
[ZERO TWO]
Not at all.
In fact, I'd love to
live like this forever.
[HIRO exhales]
I feel the same way.
I have my worries, but this
is all so new and exciting.
And...
[ZERO TWO gasps]
That's right!
I was supposed to go
bathing with the girls!
Oh, uh...
No peeking this time, darling.
[MIKU]
Did you see it? Mitsuru's hair?
[KOKORO gasps]
[MIKU chuckles] So it really
was you who cut it for him.
[KOKORO giggles]
I thought it looked
pretty good, myself.
[ICHIGO]
Mm-hm.
--A fishie!
--Hey! Hold still!
Fine...
[MIKU] You have really
pretty hair, Zero Two.
You think so?
My darling told me he thought
its color was pretty earlier.
And he said flowers the same
shade of pink would bloom soon!
Do you two always talk
about corny stuff like that,
or do you mix it up sometimes?
Now you've done it!
[MIKU yelps]
[KOKORO gasps]
Hey, watch it.
[ZERO TWO] It's my turn
to wash your hair, Miku!
[MIKU grunts]
I'll wash it myself thanks!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[MIKU gasps]
If I can't have the hair,
I guess I'll take the body!
[MIKU]
Stop! That tickles!
This is what we have, guys.
Five sources for drinking water.
And two of those sources
are only useable
if we have a means
of filtration.
There has to be some
way we can repair
the circulation systems
by ourselves.
Unfortunately, Mistilteinn
doesn't have the equipment
we need to get it
up and running.
[FUTOSHI]
And our access to the elevator
is restricted anyway, right?
Yeah.
No problem!
We'll just send a letter to Papa
and ask him to fix it for us!
I don't think there'd be any
point writing to the adults.
Yeah? And what makes
you say that, huh?
[MIKU sighs] We never
realized how big a role
the caretakers
played in our lives.
No kidding. From hot
food to clean clothes,
they always provided
our necessities.
What'll happen to us if
our rations suddenly
stop being dropped off one day?
[ICHIGO exhales]
Then the only option we'd have
would be to cook our own food!
[ALL]
Huh?
[ICHIGO gasps]
Yeah, that's right.
There's still fish
swimming in the river.
So if we could cook them...
But no one here has any
experience making food.
Because we were
never taught how to.
Actually. I think that's a
pretty good idea, as well.
Anyway,
I believe I saw some books
about cooking in the study.
[KOKORO gasps]
In that case,
maybe we could do
it after all, you guys!
[FUTOSHI]
Yeah. Maybe!
[ICHIGO]
I want to give it a shot too.
[IKUNO chuckles]
[ALL chuckle]
Then that's that!
[FUTOSHI gasps]
Hey, Zorome, look!
I thought you were
supposed to be dieting.
Why are you so gung-ho?
Uh, because it's cool?
I mean, check out how the
fire's burning everything up!
[FUTOSHI yelps]
Wow, you're right! Way cool!
Welcome back, you guys!
Look what we brought!
[ZOROME]
Talk about a haul!
[ZERO TWO giggles]
I ended up catching 11!
Really?
You did awesome!
How did you do?
Two less than what she
managed to bring in.
That's still amazing!
It is.
And Hiro?
[HIRO chuckles]
I didn't catch any fish.
[ALL laugh]
Don't worry. I'll teach you
all my tricks later, darling.
All right, next time
I'm going fishing!
[MIKU gasps]
Me too!
[ICHIGO sighs]
What're you thinking about?
Oh. Not much. Just how
the mood has changed.
[MIKU, KOKORO giggle]
When the rod twitches,
you immediately reel it in!
I don't know if I can!
Hiro was right this whole time.
I had it in my head that Zero
Two was different from us.
That she had different reasons
and goals for fighting.
I painted her as an
unapproachable enigma.
And never even tried to see
her for who she really was.
[GORO]
Ichigo.
[ICHIGO] We'll probably
never fully understand
what happened between them,
but right now,
she's an ordinary girl.
One of us. An irreplaceable
part of Squad 13.
[GORO]
Yeah. I agree.
[ICHIGO] I just want
what's best for them both.
For Zero Two... and for Hiro.
[ZOROME] We are incredible.
We cooked for ourselves!
Pretty sure you were slacking
off while we were working.
[FUTOSHI chuckles]
You never know what
you're capable of.
[HIRO]
Yeah.
[ZERO TWO giggles]
The question is
how will it taste?
We followed the
book's instructions,
so it should be fine.
Take your seats and
join me in prayer.
[ZOROME]
Forget about it.
Huh? Wait, what?
Why should we have
to pray to Papa?
We did all of the
work ourselves!
This is actually good!
Really?
Yeah, it's totally edible!
That's great!
[ZERO TWO giggles]
This is good.
Uh-huh.
Is it just me or did we
do something awesome?
I mean, there's no way
any of the other squads
have actually cooked
for themselves, right?
Yeah. We're the
only ones I know of.
You hear that? Are we a
team of geniuses or what?
Come on, Futoshi.
Eat up, it's good! Ha, ha!
Oh, boy, it's gone
to his head.
Not that we could expect
any less from him.
Right?
Doesn't he seem to be getting
a little too worked up though?
--[glass shatters]
--[ALL gasp]
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
My hands slipped and
I dropped the plate.
[ZOROME]
Hey. Quit forcing yourself.
[FUTOSHI chuckels] Oh, the mess!
I can handle clean up. It's my--
Stop it!
I know you're forcing yourself
to eat and throwing it back up.
Huh?
[FUTOSHI chuckles]
That's crazy. I'm not doing--
[ZOROME]
Don't lie to me!
Hey, cut it out.
You're wrong.
[ZOROME]
No, I'm not!
It's not like that!
[gasps]
Listen! If you wanna survive,
then you have to eat something!
[FUTOSHI gasps]
[ZOROME] Otherwise, if you
keep this up...
It's okay! I can eat!
Just watch! I'll eat it all.
[FUTOSHI chokes, coughs]
Why is this happening?
I mean, just look at what
we're going through right now.
Why hasn't Papa gotten in touch?
Why isn't he coming
here to get us all?
[MIKU gasps]
[ZOROME] You don't think...
he's cast us aside, do you?
[FUTOSHI] A part of me always
thought it wasn't our problem.
Even after I saw what
happened to Squad 26.
I was sure it wouldn't
happen to me.
As FRANXX pilots, there's
a limit to our lives.
We've always had constant
reminders of that.
[MIKIU whimpers] I...
was worried the entire time.
[MIKU] But, I was too
scared to say anything.
You're not the only one.
I had my fears too but
kept them to myself.
[ICHIGO]
Same.
Okay. I've been writing
letters this whole month.
Letting Nana and Hachi
know how we're doing.
But, they never
accepted a single one.
The heck. You already tried?
You guys. Assuming we really
have been cast aside by Papa
and the others,
I think that we're fine.
As long as I'm with all of you,
I'm not worried about
what's in store for us
because if we're together,
we can make it work out.
Look at today. We cooked our
own food, and it was fun.
Whether it's creating meals or
discussing how to go about
our daily lives,
we've never spent time
together like this before.
I never said I wasn't
having fun. It's just that...
You're right.
Before today, fighting was
all we'd ever known.
Yeah! I had fun too!
Though I couldn't
quite finish my food.
We can make more
whenever we want.
Yeah. Mitsuru's right
about that.
[HIRO]
Whether it's cooking as a group,
taking baths, or
talking things out,
I'm finding so much joy
and value in it. All of it.
It's making me feel like this
place is truly where we belong.
You think so?
I'm certain our lives
have some purpose beyond
piloting the FRANXX.
There's more.
[MITSURU sighs]
[FUTOSHI whimpers]
Futoshi.
Oh, come on!
What're you crying for?
Like you're one to talk!
[ZOROME]
Shaddup!
[stomach growls]
Ugh. And of course
now I feel hungry.
[MIKU giggles]
Better late than never.
[ZOROME] That's more like it!
Eat up! You need the energy!
Being a fatty is
what suits you best.
[FUTOSHI] Seriously, Zorome!
You better stop calling me that.
[FUTOSHI] That day, we cried
and laughed together,
more than we ever had before.
[HIRO]
"Humans! Humans!
They have neither
the wings to fly,
nor the claws or fangs to hunt.
Such weak and frail creatures.
But, they are so, so warm.
Humans are wonderful."
[HIRO]
Wait, aren't these from...
[ZERO TWO] Yeah. The picture
book we read together.
You remember every page?
That's amazing.
Although, the story's
kinda sad, isn't it?
[ZERO TWO]
You think?
It was the first "pretty thing"
I could ever really
say was mine.
[ZERO TWO]
Then we met,
and I wanted to have
something beautiful with you.
[ZERO TWO] You showed me
the outside world after all.
But this entire time,
I didn't really understand
what it meant to be human.
Eventually, I was
made to realize
that it wasn't about
appearances at all.
You guys shine too
brightly in my eyes.
You cry and laugh and get mad.
Try to live together as a group.
And then I came, and you
let me be a part of that.
Darling, I realized this is
what I've been searching for.
The kind of humanity
I wanted all along.
Zero Two.
[HIRO] Don't worry.
We'll be together forever.
[roaring]
♪