[clapping]
I've been chosen, to represent
all of us children.
My code is Zero-One-Six. I...
[MITSURU] Don't... Don't give
him that look of admiration.
[MITSURU]
He's a filthy traitor!
[gasps]
[ZOROME] That's unusual.
You never oversleep.
Did you have a nice dream?
Your face is red.
[MITSURU grunts]
[ZOROME]
Well, we're gonna head down.
[FUTOSHI]
Man, I'm starving!
[MITSURU] If you place
your hopes in anything,
they will be betrayed.
Promises will go unfulfilled,
and faith will be let down.
Which is why I swore to myself,
that I wouldn't expect anything
from anyone anymore.
That way, I would
never be hurt again.
[door clatters]
♪
[ICHIGO]
We killed 25 in total today.
They were all the same
type of Conrad-class,
just like on the other days.
Thanks for the report.
Due to all of your efforts,
the S-Planning occurring
in this area has been
proceeding quite smoothly.
[HACHI] That said, you need
to improve your kill count,
codes Three-Two-Six
and One-Nine-Six.
Your Parasite Score
is dropping, too.
I just wasn't feeling
very well today.
[HACHI] That's not
enough to explain this.
Anyway, let's keep it up and
continue to defend the work
area going forward.
That is all. Dismissed.
Twenty-five more.
That takes their grand total
in this area to over 90.
That's right. Their number of
kills over the past fortnight
is 3.7 times greater
than in their first.
It'd be unthinkable
for any other team
to achieve such rapid growth.
If their puberty and
competitive spirit,
the very things you previously
referred to as "problems,"
are what's drawing out the full
abilities of these children.
It can't be.
That would be a total refutation
of our prior methods.
Yes, but what if that's
what Dr. Franxx is after?
[ZOROME] What are
they even doing here?
Nana called it
S-Planning, I think?
I would guess they're
digging for something.
That is an excavator, right?
[ZERO TWO]
It's probably nothing good.
[HIRO]
Uh?
[ZERO TWO] I'm about to choke
from the stench of klaxosaurs.
To think we get to be
on this special mission.
It just goes to show how
much stronger we've gotten.
Which we owe entirely to you.
You always try so hard
to help carry my burden.
Well, of course I do!
If anything were to
ever happen to you,
it'd be my responsibility!
[KOKORO chuckles]
Thanks for that, Futoshi.
Uh... Kokoro. Um.
Y'know, I was thinking...
I'm gonna keep working
to be the best partner
you could possibly have.
So, uh, do you think you
could maybe promise to be
my partner for the
rest of forever?
[KOKORO giggles]
Of course. I promise.
Really? You mean it?
Then, it's a promise!
I will always protect you!
[MIKU]
Please stop.
You're starting to gross
me out over here.
[FUTOSHI]
Huh?
Just cut the comms. I can
feel my ears rotting off.
[FUTOSHI] You overheard
all of that? Not cool!
[alarms blaring]
[ICHIGO] Seven enemies
closing in from nine o'clock.
More of those same Conrad-class.
[GORO] Again? Do they
have a nest nearby?
[ICHIGO]
All units, prepare for combat!
[IKUNO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
What's the matter, Chlorophytum?
Hey, Mitsuru! Mitsuru?
[HACHI] The Child Fever.
It came sooner than expected.
Good thing the others
could take out the enemy
without Chlorophytum.
[NANA] For now, I'll give
him an antipyretic.
It's only a stopgap measure,
but it should show some
results by tomorrow.
[HACHI] Code Three-Two-Six
has already had the procedure?
[GORO] Mitsuru's always
had a frail body.
That may be true, but he's
the only one who received
that injection and
came back afterwards.
What are you talking about?
The Elixir Injection.
It's a drug that induces more
yellow blood cell production.
And it greatly increases one's
parasite aptitude, as well.
[MIKU] All that aside, has
Mitsuru always been so moody?
No, he didn't used to be.
In fact, he followed
Hiro around a lot.
No way! That's the biggest
shocker I've heard in a while!
So how did he go from that
to butting heads with him
over every little
thing all the time?
I don't know. Sorry.
But it couldn't have
started too long
before he took
the injection.
[gasps] Actually, now
that I think about it,
Hiro changed a bit
back then, too.
The Elixir Injection.
It has a survival rate of
only 15 percent, right?
Goodness. I didn't know he'd
been through something so risky.
[MITSURU breathes heavily]
[MITSURU]
I wanna be like you, Hiro.
[MITSURU] I wanna fight
together with you in a FRANXX.
But they say that I can't
if I stay like this,
'cause I'm too weak.
If I take that injection and
come back alive, though...
Hiro, will you pilot a
FRANXX with me then?
[MITSURU gasps, pants]
Damn it!
[NANA] Okay, you seem to be
out of the woods for now.
Let me pilot a FRANXX.
It might be too early.
Wait until--
Let me pilot.
[NANA exhales]
[HACHI]
This doesn't look good.
If things continue like this,
he may become a pruning target.
[ALL]
A "partner shuffle"?
This isn't an order. Merely an
option available to you.
Take this opportunity to
discuss it with your partners,
and if anyone wants
to try the shuffle, ask.
[FUTOSHI] The two of us
definitely don't need
to do this. After all,
I've already promised to protect
you forever. Right, Kokoro?
[KOKORO]
Mh-hm.
[HIRO] Zero Two, is something
bothering you?
You must remember. I told
you to speak your mind,
and not hold anything back,
because I want to
get to know you better.
Oh, did you?
Yeah. When you're
feeling down, I'm here.
So if something's weighing on
your mind. Please, tell me--
Honestly, that sounds
like a real pain.
We can understand each other
just fine by piloting Strelizia.
[MITSURU]
Hmph.
[IKUNO] Give it a rest.
You do know what caused this
entire mess,
don't you, Mitsuru?
What are you trying to say?
Would you drop the act?
That's enough. Stop.
[IKUNO]
It takes courage to face others,
not to mention yourself.
What's your point?
[IKUNO]
You want to be acknowledged,
but not by Papa or the adults.
Shut up! I told you to drop it!
[MITSURU]
Tsk.
That's much better.
Acting cool and aloof
doesn't suit you.
But, as we know,
I'm not like you.
[NANA] So then, is there anyone
who wants to try riding with
a different partner?
I would like to attempt a
pistil-to-pistil connection.
[NANA]
Pistil-to-pistil? But...
I wanna try it so we
can have a backup
in emergencies where
we've lost a stamen.
Ichigo, would you help me?
Huh? Wait, me?
Pretty please.
[ICHIGO sighs]
Sure, I guess.
All right. Let's
try it. Anyone else?
[NANA gasps]
I'd like to try
riding with Mitsuru.
[ALL gasp]
But... Kokoro.
What about our promise?
[FUTOSHI whimpers]
I'm sorry, Futoshi.
[sobs]
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
One hundred sixty seconds
since connection commenced.
Both units show no
change in numbers.
Well, Ichigo?
I don't feel it.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Delphinium's numbers
remain unchanged. Timing out.
[computer beeps]
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Genista's score has crossed
the minimum required.
It remains in the lower range,
but is stable.
I suppose that'll do.
For now, at least.
[ICHIGO]
So much for that.
It was a good idea you had,
but I knew it wouldn't
work without a boy.
[IKUNO]
I was serious, you know.
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
Go ahead and laugh
if you must.
[FUTOSHI sobs] Why?
Did I do something wrong?
I tried my hardest
for Kokoro's sake!
Well, maybe that was
getting on her nerves.
Or maybe you need to lose
some weight. Who knows?
Regardless, I wonder what
Kokoro was thinking.
She's such a nice person, she
must've felt bad for Mitsuru.
Especially since
he's so miserable.
I'm clearly the most
miserable one here!
[GORO]
Calm down, man!
Hold it! Do you
think I'm pathetic?
Easy, Futoshi.
What difference does
this really make?
It doesn't matter
who our partners are.
[FUTOSHI grunts] Like you'd
have any idea how I feel!
What a nuisance.
Mitsuru, try to understand
where he's coming from.
[MITSURU grunts]
What gives you the
right to say that?
[HIRO gasps]
[FUTOSHI sobs]
[FUTOSHI] Whenever I
think about Kokoro,
I feel this tightness
in my chest.
But now that tightness
really hurts.
It hurts so bad.
What is this feeling?
I hear you.
[KOKORO humming]
[KOKORO] Look! Flowers.
Don't they smell nice?
What are you playing at?
[KOKORO gasps]
Oh, Mitsuru.
Why do you think it is humans
stopped having children?
Probably because we
don't need to anymore.
[KOKORO]
Really? But in the past,
wasn't having a baby
the most natural thing?
You shouldn't waste
time thinking about
something unnecessary.
Just one look at the
adults makes it clear.
The simple truth is,
we don't need others to live.
Why did you volunteer
to be my partner?
Futoshi hates me now,
and it's a massive pain.
Was it out of pity?
It wasn't! No,
it's nothing like that.
Hey, listen, Mitsuru,
you should--
[alarms blaring]
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] We've
detected what appears to be
a Gutenberg-class klaxosaur
to the south-southwest.
It's approaching us at
80 kilometers per hour.
Set up a defensive line 500
meters from the S-Planning
and neutralize the target.
Genista and Chlorophytum
will act as rear support.
[FUTOSHI] Mitsuru! Promise me,
that you'll protect Kokoro,
no matter what!
"Promise you"? Ridiculous.
Why you!
Wait, it's fine.
I'll be all right, Futoshi.
[FUTOSHI grunts] Just be
careful out there, Kokoro.
What's done is done, okay?
I'll do my best with Ikuno.
[KOKORO]
Hm.
So you do... your best--
[FUTOSHI sobs]
[IKUNO sighs]
[KLAXASAUR roars]
[MIKU]
That thing is huge!
[ZERO TWO]
Finally, one worth fighting!
[ICHIGO]
Hang on!
[ZERO TWO shouts]
No good. The core's
too deep inside.
[ZERO TWO]
Sounds like fun!
[HIRO]
Zero Two, wait!
[ZERO TWO]
Hm?
[ICHIGO, MIKU grunt]
[ICHIGO]
You okay?
[ZERO TWO]
Mind your own business!
[MIKU]
Ugh, that girl.
[MIKU gasps]
Where'd these come from?
[ZERO TWO grunts]
It's a collective mass.
This thing's made up
of those Conrad-class
we've been fighting.
And when attacked, they
recombine and close the opening.
[ICHIGO, MIKU gasp]
[ZERO TWO]
You damn monster!
[HIRO grunts]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[ZERO TWO]
Don't stop me, darling!
[HIRO] Just calm down!
Don't rush it!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[HIRO]
What do we do, Ichigo?
We'll never get
anywhere like this.
[KOKORO]
We need to shoot at it.
Genista could separate
that klaxosaur
with a blast of
close-range fire.
[MIKU] Nice idea!
That'll expose the core!
Go ahead and fire
a round into it!
[ICHIGO] Back up, that plan is
too risky for Genista right now.
[KOKORO]
All of our lives are at risk.
We're a team, aren't we?
[FUTOSHI sobs]
[ICHIGO]
Fine. But don't get reckless.
[KOKORO]
Roger.
[klaxasaur roars]
[ICHIGO]
No! Some got past us!
[IKUNO]
Let's go.
[KOKORO]
Mm!
Ikuno, you're way too tense.
Loosen up a bit.
[IKUNO gasps, grunts]
[MITSURU grunts]
[KOKORO] There's no
need to rush, Mitsuru.
I know what I'm doing!
[HIRO]
You okay?
[KOKORO]
Yeah, thank you, Hiro.
Mitsuru. Hang in there.
Why are you always so damn--!
[KOKORO]
Ah! Mitsuru!
[FUTOSHI]
Kokoro!
Genista's positive
pulse is dropping.
It's going below minimum.
[KOKORO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
Run away!
[KOKORO gasps]
[IKUNO grunts]
Are you all right?
I am now! Thanks,
Ikuno and Futoshi.
[ICHIGO] Okay, change of plans!
Miku and I will stop this thing!
[MIKU] Chlorophytum,
take care of Genista!
No matter what,
I will protect Kokoro!
Come on, Mitsuru,
let's try to start over.
[MITSURU]
Aw, forget it.
If you place your hopes in me,
you'll only be let down.
I'm completely incompetent.
[KOKORO]
You're wrong!
You're not incompetent
at all, you hear me?
[HACHI]
What are you doing, Genista?
Recommence connecting!
Do you realize the situ--?
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] Genista has
entered radio silence.
What could they
possibly be thinking?
[KOKORO] Mitsuru, you can
rely on others more, you know.
Despite what you think,
I believe in you.
So I want you to try
to believe in me, too.
[MITSURU exhales]
You're kidding me.
Hiro, will you pilot a
FRANXX with me then?
Yeah. I promise I will!
[MITSURU gasps]
[MITSURU] Hiro. I gave it
my all. I'm stronger now.
I can fight with you.
I kept my end of our promise...
with you... Hiro, I...
"Our promise"?
What promise was that?
[MITSURU] Believing in someone
else will only get you betrayed!
I was a fool for ever
expecting anything from him!
So why? Why make that promise
if you were just gonna
forget about it?
[ZERO TWO shouts]
You were deeply hurt by him
back then, weren't you?
So deeply that one normally
wouldn't be able to recover.
[KOKORO]
But you know,
I've betrayed and hurt
somebody else, as well.
I've even broken a promise.
I'm not the nice, gentle girl
that you all think I am.
That's why, if I ever
found myself betrayed
by someone like that,
I'd have no right to complain.
I couldn't blame them
for what they had done.
So, what? I should
just forgive him?
That's something you have
to decide for yourself.
What I'm trying to say is,
as awful as it may be,
these things happen with us.
We children aren't perfect
like the adults are.
But still, I wanna have
relationships with people.
I want to laugh and cry
together with others.
[IKUNO]
Mitsuru. Hurry!
[KOKORO] So like I said before,
I believe in you.
[MITSURU gasps]
What are you?
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Genista's negative pulse ratio
is rising rapidly.
At this rate, it will
transition to stampede mode.
It's too dangerous for
you kids! Stop it, now!
[IKUNO]
Kokoro, don't!
[KOKORO screams]
Kokoro!
[KOKORO grunting]
Kokoro, you have to stop!
Mitsuru, why'd you...?
You do the craziest
things sometimes, don't you?
But I...
How come? How can you trust
somebody else so much?
Doesn't it scare you?
[KOKORO chuckles]
You are unbelievable.
[KOKORO] Hey, everyone,
sorry we're so late!
[ALL]
Kokoro!
About time, Mitsuru.
[shouts]
[FUTOSHI shouts]
[MITSURU shouts]
Let's go!
[KOKORO]
Now!
[HIRO grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[FUTOSHI] Hey, Mitsuru! Do you
realize how dangerous that was?
Futoshi.
Why'd you make Kokoro do that?
[KOKORO]
Mitsuru!
Why didn't you dodge that punch?
Don't you see how
unreasonable you're being?
You're supposed to be a man!
Well, hurting a girl is
the worst possible thing
any man can ever do!
If you make Kokoro cry,
I'm gonna make you pay,
you understand?!
I promise you...
[FUTOSHI gasps]
I promise I will protect Kokoro,
from this point on.
That's what you wanted. Happy?
Mitsuru.
[FUTOSHI whimpers]
But I... loved Kokoro so much.
I loved her so much!
[FUTOSHI crying]
You don't worry about that.
The two of us will
always be together.
Until we die, my darling.
[MITSURU] She told me,
"As awful as it may be,
these things
happen with us,"
and she was
probably right.
[MITSURU] I don't know if I'll
ever be able to forgive Hiro,
but... I do know that
these kinds of things
will surely continue to
happen between all of us.
[MITSURU] When I woke
up the next morning,
my temperature was
back to normal.
♪