[alarms blarring]
[NANA]
This is bad.
The depths of
their consciousnesses
will connect through
Strelizia and merge!
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO] That room was the
entirety of my world. A closed
world that would never touch
what lay outside those windows.
[HIRO] That place was
the entirety of my world.
The Garden, a closed world
where only children lived.
[ZERO TWO] But that day, I went
outside for the first time.
To this day,
I haven't forgotten.
[HIRO] To this day,
I'd forgotten all about...
[ZERO TWO]
How vast the sky above was.
[HIRO]
How warm the hand I held was.
[HIRO, ZERO TWO] And the promise
that we made to each other.
[ZERO TWO]
"Who exactly am I?"
Back then, that question
never even crossed my mind.
I was trapped in that room for
as far back as I can remember.
I felt like I had
older memories,
but I soon forgot them.
[ZERO TWO]
I didn't know what this was.
Probably a stand-in for what
you would call a mother.
[ZERO TWO] One day,
for the first and only time,
she brought me something
that wasn't food.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
It was a picture book.
As I turned the pages, its
bright colors jumped out at me,
as did various shapes.
It had words, too, but I
couldn't understand them.
And after that day,
she never showed up again.
Anyway, this book was
my first "pretty thing."
The outside world surely
contained many more.
At least, that's what
I innocently believed
in that moment.
It turns out that I was
half-right... and half-wrong.
[HIRO]
Who exactly am I? Back then,
that question was the only
thing I ever had on my mind.
I was in the Garden for as
far back as I can remember.
We lived there in order
to become parasites
who would fight on behalf
of Papa and the others.
All of us children were referred
to by our code numbers.
The lower the number,
the higher the child's
potential as a parasite.
The double-digits,
up through Zero-Nine-Nine,
were given special treatment.
Particularly the teens.
I was one of them, and I
was told that I was special,
unlike everyone else.
[HIRO gasps]
[ICHIGO whimpers]
[HIRO]
Are you crying?
[ICHIGO]
Am I... a weirdo?
[HIRO]
Uh...?
[ICHIGO] I mean, I'm not
like everybody else.
[ICHIGO] The others have
all stopped smiling.
They don't get mad or
cry anymore, either.
But I... I still shed tears.
I just wanna be
like everyone else!
So what am I supposed to do?
[ICHIGO sobs]
Should I get more injections?
Well, y'know, both our
codes are in the teens,
so we were already different
from them to begin with.
[ICHIGO] I don't want that.
Being different is scary.
[ICHIGO sniffs]
I know. How'd you like
me to give you a name?
[ICHIGO]
Huh? A name?
[HIRO]
Mm-hm. I gave myself a name
and I believe you should
have one, as well.
A totally unique name. Like the
kind the people in books have,
and not just a number.
Wanna know my name? It's Hiro!
Hiro?
So whadda ya say? You'll feel
better that way, right?
If I give you one,
you'll be like me!
[ICHIGO gasps]
'Kay.
Then your name'll be... Hm...
Ichigo!
Huh? Why Ichigo?
[HIRO] Well, because!
That's what came to mind
when I thought about
your number. Ichigo.
So that's my name now? "Ichigo"?
[HIRO]
Mm-hm! What do you think?
[HIRO] Having your own
name can make you feel like
it's okay to be different.
[ICHIGO]
Really?
[HIRO] Yep, because it's a
unique name that exists
for you alone.
For me and no one else?
Yeah. Ichigo.
[gasps]
Do you think you could give
the other kids names, too?
[HIRO]
Uh. Sure.
Well then, let's get everyone
in on this! So, uh...
C'mon, Hiro! You've gotta
think up names for all of them!
[HIRO]
It was just a game.
I gave names to many
of the children.
Samii, Junna, Nakku, Toshi,
Sakuto, Shinya, and Mitsuru.
A name is but one way
to refer to a person.
But just having one made us
feel our anxieties fade away.
What are you kids doing?
You're not allowed to
change your designation
without permission.
[KIDS gasp]
But what's so bad about
giving ourselves names?
[BOTH gasp]
That boy is.
One of the teen codes.
[MALE STAFF 13A] Anyway, don't
go doing things as you please.
[door hisses]
[ICHIGO sighs]
[HIRO grunts]
[HIRO] The adults never
answered my questions,
and the other children
never asked any.
[HIRO] Children were gradually
disappearing from the Garden
at regular intervals.
And the adults never
told us where they went.
[HIRO]
Meanwhile, I was designated
a special research subject,
and underwent tests at
the Lab all by myself.
[HIRO] If I did well,
I was given a reward.
But, even then,
there was still no one who
would answer my questions.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Whoa, horns?
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO grunting]
[FRANXX]
Marvelous.
She's leagues better than
all of our past specimens.
I can't believe she's
developed such a human form.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[screams]
[FRANXX]
Ooh! Look! How amazing!
You are an amazing child!
[HIRO] Who was that
girl with the horns?
Another question.
That's not for you to know.
Now return to
your room, at once.
[HIRO] That was the first time I
had seen a child with red horns.
And now there was another thing
I wanted to know more about.
I've got it!
[HIRO]
If no one would answer me,
I could just go find
out for myself.
[LAB MAN 13A] You there.
That's not the way to the lobby.
Oh.
I should've figured it
wouldn't be that easy.
I don't see any
back doors, either.
[sighs]
Never thought it'd
be so difficult
to look for
something on my own.
[gasps]
[HIRO]
That's her!
[HIRO grunts]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[gasps]
[FEMALE STAFF 13B sighs]
[door hisses]
[HIRO gasps]
Incredible. Wow!
[HIRO] For some reason, it made
me really, really happy.
[HIRO]
Mitsuru!
[MITSURU]
Mm? Oh, uh... Hi, Hiro.
Are you going to the Lab?
[MITSURU]
Yeah.
[HIRO]
What's the matter?
[MITSURU]
I'm going to get an injection.
[HIRO]
Uh?
[MITSURU] If I don't,
I won't be able to stay.
[HIRO] All of the children in
the Garden knew exactly
what it meant to get
an Elixir Injection.
While you could expect a
drastic improvement in your
aptitude scores, it had an
incredibly low success rate.
And if it failed,
you wouldn't come back.
I wanna become a
parasite with you, Hiro,
and fight alongside you.
Uh, wait. With me?
[MITSURU] If I come back alive,
will you pilot with me?
Yeah, of course I will!
[MITSURU gasps]
[BOY 13A]
Again?
[GIRL 13A]
It's Four-Nine-Four this time.
[BOY 13A] It was
Three-Six-Seven before that.
[GIRL 13A]
We just spoke yesterday.
[BOY 13A]
Papa threw them away.
[GIRL 13A]
Will I be next? I'm scared!
[HIRO exhales]
We've gotta do something.
Huh? Hold on. You know
Papa made the decision.
Which means there's nothing
we can do about it.
[MALE STAFF 13B]
Code Zero-One-Six.
You should be getting ready.
[HIRO grunts] I wanna know,
where do the kids go when they--
Get ready.
[HIRO]
But what about my question?
[HIRO gasps]
[LAB MAN 13B] His sensitivity
is becoming a problem.
[LAB MAN 13C] It might
affect the other children.
[LAB MAN 13D]
Shouldn't we increase his
yellow blood cell dose?
[FRANXX]
Leave it as is.
[LAB MAN 13E]
Sir?
[FRANXX] I'm very interested
in what kind of parasite
a child like him
will grow up to be.
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO screaming]
[screaming continues]
[HIRO gasps]
[MALE STAFF 13B]
What are you doing here?
Return to the Garden.
Uh... You have to make
it stop, she's in pain!
[MALE STAFF 13B] That's none of
your business. Come with me.
Uh! But...! Uh, but!
[HIRO] But... the list of
things I wanted to know
continued to grow
in number. Who are we?
Why can't we give
ourselves names?
Where do the kids
who disappear go?
Will Mitsuru come back?
Who is that girl?
Why don't the adults
give me any answers?
Why isn't anyone else
asking questions?
[HIRO]
Why is she...?
[ZERO TWO breathes heavily]
[door hisses]
[gasps]
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO] I didn't understand
anything... but...
Hey, get away from the window!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[HIRO]
Come this way!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[HIRO]
I can get you out of here!
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[HIRO] But you...
you smiled back then.
[HIRO] In this world where
questions and answers
fell on deaf ears...
[gasps]
[HIRO] ...you shone
so brightly in my eyes.
[ZERO TWO] That was my first
experience of the outside world.
It was covered in
white and cold.
[ZERO TWO, HIRO grunt]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[ZERO TWO] Everything around
me was unfamiliar.
[snow crunches]
[bird chirps]
[ZERO TWO growls]
[mice squeak]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[HIRO grunts, gasps]
[HIRO gasps]
Wha--What are you eating?
No, hold on.
Don't swallow it!
Spit it out!
[ZERO TWO growls]
Uh! Ow!
[growling continues]
[HIRO gasps]
You meanie, I was
only tryin' to--!
[ZERO TWO whimpers]
Wait a second, do you not
understand what I'm saying?
I'm Code Zero-One-Six. Hiro.
What's your code number?
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[HIRO] Aw, man, does she
not understand me at all?
Oh, hey, you're barefoot.
[HIRO]
Zero-Zero-Two?
I've never seen a code
in the single digits.
Zero-Zero-Two. Hm... Oni?
Nah, Zero Two, maybe?
No, that's not very good either.
Eo-oo!
[HIRO gasps]
Wait, you know what names are?
Eo-oo! Eo-oo! Eo-oo!
I really should've come up
with something better.
[HIRO chuckles]
Let's go, Zero Two.
Let's go somewhere far away!
[grunts]
[ZERO TWO]
I didn't understand his words,
but I knew that his
voice called to me.
I saw things with him.
I walked with him.
And every moment we shared,
was so much fun.
[HIRO]
Here you go.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
It's food, eat it.
Oh, wait a second.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Now say, "Aah!"
Aah...
[ZERO TWO squeals]
[HIRO laughs]
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Ah!
What? Are you sure
I can look at it?
[ZERO TWO]
Ah!
[HIRO chuckles]
Well, thank you.
[HIRO] The Beast and
the Prince , huh?
Wow! These pictures
are so pretty!
Now, let's see. "In the deepest,
darkest part of a forest
lived a tribe, hidden--"
[MALE GUARD 13A]
Yeah. No doubt about it.
They're in this area.
They should still be
nearby. Look for them.
[MALE GUARD 13B, MALE GUARD 13C]
Sir.
[ZERO TWO growls]
It's okay. Just relax.
They'll let us off if--
[MALE GUARD 13C] What do
we do about Zero-One-Six?
[MALE GUARD 13A]
Zero-Zero-Two takes priority.
If he resists, you may kill him.
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
Mm?
[HIRO] Don't worry.
I'm here. I'll protect you.
[HIRO] "In the deepest,
darkest part of a forest,
lived a strong and
beautiful beast princess.
Beckoned by the moonlight,
she wandered into a
country of humans,
and in the moonlit garden
of a small castle,
she fell in love with a prince.
But the princess was a beast.
She had ashen wings on her back.
Not knowing what to do,
she went to see a witch
who lived at the
edge of the forest,
and said, 'I want to
live as a human.
I want to be united with him.'
The witch replied like so,
'I can help you, if you offer
me your wings.
But, keep this in mind.
No matter how you disguise
yourself, you are a beast,
and you will consume the
prince's life one day.'"
Sorry. I was just thinking
how sad this story is.
Is it only because one of them
isn't human that the prince and
the princess can't get married?
[ZERO TWO]
Awwi?
[HIRO] Yeah. That's what
it's called when two people
who love each other promise
to be together forever.
Or at least, it would be
if they were both human.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[HIRO sighs] Well.
C'mon, let's walk some more.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Are you okay? Let me see.
[HIRO gasps]
It's blue?
Uh, anyway, I need
something to--
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Endure it, okay?
I read in a book that animals
lick their wounds to heal them.
And it's all I've got.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Awwi?
[HIRO gasps]
Awwi. Awwi?
[HIRO chuckles]
Once we get outta here,
'cause I wanna be
with you forever, too.
And that way I can always be...
...darling.
[gasps]
Da...
[ZERO TWO] I don't know why,
but tears flowed from my eyes.
It wasn't because my wound hurt.
It's a mistletoe.
[ZERO TWO] Yeah, those were
probably tears of joy.
The picture book's
world was pretty,
and I believed that if I was
with him, I could be the same.
[ZERO TWO]
But, this world didn't allow it.
[HIRO]
Why? Why is it?
Am I not able to find
the answers I seek...
...because I'm just a child,
who doesn't have the power
to protect anyone?
[ZERO TWO] Why didn't I
realize that he and I
were different creatures,
with blood of different colors,
and that I... was a monster?
[MALE GUARD 13A]
That's what you get...
[FRANXX] Erase those memories.
They're noise.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling!
[ICHIGO] Aren't you gonna
give them names anymore?
[MITSURU]
You liar!
[NANA]
This is bad.
[MALE VOICE 13A]
Monster.
[ZERO TWO] So, that's why
I swore to become human,
no matter what it took,
or what I had to do.
If I were the same as him,
I could be with him forever.
[ALL]
Delphinium!
[ICHIGO screams]
[ICHIGO] Hiro, get away
from Zero Two, right now!
She only got closer to you so
that she could suck you dry!
If you stay with her, even you
will lose your humanity!
[ZERO TWO]
That's right. After all, I...
[HIRO]
The picture book.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
That was you. You were the girl.
The one with the
picture book back then.
[ZERO TWO gasps]