[MITSURU grunts]
[KOKORO gasps]
Good morning.
Beautiful, isn't it?
[KOKORO]
Mm.
♪
We will abandon
Mistilteinn shortly,
so be ready to leave...
at any time.
Abandon it? But it's so sudden.
The situation has changed.
When the next
supply ship arrives,
we will be boarding it to be
taken to the parasite camp.
[ICHIGO]
After ignoring us for so long,
where is this coming from?
[ICHIGO] So they were
watching us the whole time.
--[HIRO] You okay?
--[GORO grunts]
[HIRO]
How's your fever?
Oh. It's no big deal,
don't worry.
[HIRO] Miku came down
with one recently, too.
Uh-huh. Goes to show
we all have our issues.
[HIRO grunts]
[door hisses]
[GORO gasps]
What's wrong, Ichigo?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[GORO]
"Abandon it," huh?
[ICHIGO] Can we not
just stay here somehow?
We only have rations for
a few more days at best.
Besides, Mistilteinn itself
won't be able to
last much longer.
[HIRO grunts]
[GORO]
Y'know, looking back at it,
our life here wasn't that bad.
Yeah, but now we can't
stay here anymore.
And that's... kinda sad.
Hey, guys?
There's something I'd like us
to do, while we're still here.
[GORO, ICHIGO gasp]
[ALL]
A wedding?
Uh, what's that?
[HIRO] It was a ceremony
where two humans of old
would make a solemn vow.
To be true to each other,
in sickness and in health,
and to never part until death.
That's what it means to marry.
At least according to this book.
And, who do you see getting
married at this thing?
[HIRO]
Kokoro and Mitsuru.
[ALL gasp]
Well, when Hiro
told us about it,
we thought it sounded
truly wonderful.
We decided to do it here,
before we all have
to leave this place.
[KOKORO giggles]
fter how they yelled at you,
you've got some
nerve tryin' this.
That sounds so romantic!
You guys have my full support!
I'm not sure I really get it.
But it seems like a good way to
make one last memory here, so--
[FUTOSHI grunts]
Futoshi, listen. I know...
[ALL gasp]
[FUTOSHI]
Then I'm taking this role!
I don't care what
you say, I'm doing it!
I-I wanna be right beside
Kokoro and Mitsuru
so I can be the first person
to congratulate them!
Futoshi. Thank you.
[GORO] We'll have to get
to work right away
if we're gonna pull this off.
[ALL]
Right!
[KOKORO]
That's the wedding dress?
Yep. You wear that
for the ceremony.
Wow...
Do you really think that we're
gonna be able to make it?
What material can we use?
[MIKU grunts]
Turning the curtains
into a dress.
You sure do come up
with some crazy ideas.
Well, they're white,
aren't they?
Which is just what we need.
[MIKU gasps]
Our potential, to leave a mark.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[GORO]
What are these?
They're rings.
Apparently we exchange them
during the ceremony.
Huh. That sounds nice.
And I bet Kokoro will love it.
[MITSURU sighs]
I sure hope so.
That should be enough
chairs, don't you think so?
[HIRO]
Uh-huh.
[ZOROME]
Hiro!
[HIRO grunts]
Pass it back!
So, y'know, don'tcha wanna
make this a bit more grand?
Grand, how?
[MIKU] Hey! There's no
time to play around!
[ZOROME] Oh, quit being a nag!
I was about to get to work!
[MIKU] Good, 'cause there's
still a lot of preparations
for you to help out with!
[door clatters]
Ikuno, are you awake?
[ICHIGO]
Still feeling under the weather?
Do you have a fever?
[IKUNO]
You don't have to worry.
It's nothing like that.
[ICHIGO sighs]
Listen.
During the time the
Nines were visiting,
did something happen?
Huh?
[ICHIGO] I'd never
seen you get so angry.
At least, not like that before.
[IKUNO grunts]
Nothing, really.
Uh, sorry. I know it's rude
of me to pry. But I get it.
If that didn't make us mad,
then it's hard to
imagine anything would.
Anyway, I appreciate
you doing that
for Kokoro and Mitsuru.
[IKUNO] You're wrong.
I didn't do it for them.
Then why did you?
[IKUNO]
You wanna know?
Are you really that
interested in me?
Ikuno... what?
[gasps]
[IKUNO]
At that moment,
I was thinking the same
thing as the Nines.
And when I slapped Alpha, it was
in order to hide that fact.
[ICHIGO] What do you mean,
"the same thing"?
FRANXX can only be operated
by a boy and a girl.
And I've always wished
that stupid system
would just go to hell forever.
Ikuno...
[IKUNO]
But you know what I realized?
As much as I find it a pain,
I wouldn't be myself if I
refused to acknowledge it.
You wouldn't be who
you are without it.
And I would hate that.
So...
[IKUNO sobs]
What is wrong with me?
My feelings are such a mess!
Your feelings?
[IKUNO]
Ichigo, I love you.
[ICHIGO gasps]
Why me? Of all people?
[IKUNO] Because, you're the
one who gave me my name.
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
[BOY A]
I got it! "Ikuro".
[GIRL A giggles]
That's so weird!
[IKUNO] Remember how
everyone tried to follow
in Hiro's footsteps, and started
giving each other names?
[ICHIGO]
No.
[IKUNO gasps]
Your name's "Ikuno". Good?
[IKUNO] I bet you think
it's a silly reason.
But, ever since
that day back then,
I've only had eyes for you.
[IKUNO] You changed your
hairclip a while ago,
didn't you?
[ICHIGO gasps]
Yeah.
I notice these kinds
of things about you.
Did you lose the old one?
Or is this from a
certain somebody?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[IKUNO]
I'm a creep, aren't I?
I mean,
I get so jealous of the boys
who get to stand beside you,
because they're
boys and I'm not.
I wanna keep you all to myself.
That's so selfish.
It's a pain, right?
Why am I like this? Why am I?
[IKUNO sobs]
I hate being like this!
[ICHIGO] Oh. I see.
She's just like I used to be.
[IKUNO gasps]
Ichigo?
[ICHIGO] There's nothing
wrong with being a pain.
In fact, I'm a pretty
big one myself.
We all are.
Complicated difficult pains.
But, y'know, I've started
thinking that it's actually
all right for us to be this way.
I get the feeling that
going through this stuff
and having these
experiences is what life is
supposed to be all about.
You know, I prob'ly won't be
able to give up very easily.
I don't often accept "no."
[ICHIGO]
Yeah, I do.
[IKUNO]
Ichigo, thank you.
[ZOROME]
All right!
Everyone ready?
[ZERO TWO]
Mm?
[roaring]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[MALE PARTNERS groan]
[groaning continues]
[ZERO TWO gasps, grunts]
[roaring]
[gasps]
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[gasps]
You okay? What's the matter?
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[sighs] I guess I dozed off.
[HIRO grunts]
Oh, wow. It looks like
it's almost completed.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Almost. Then I'll come show it
to you as soon as it's finished.
Great.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling, you were right.
They're in full bloom now.
Look.
Kokoro let me borrow this outfit
to wear for the wedding. See?
[HIRO] It's kinda funny to
see you wearing our uniform.
Is that all you have to say?
[HIRO chuckles]
It looks great on you.
[ZERO TWO giggles]
[ZERO TWO]
You remember, right?
All those years ago,
we promised each other
that we'd get married
one day as well.
[HIRO]
Of course.
[ZERO TWO] A marriage is when
two people who love each other
promise to be
together forever.
You taught me that.
And what's more, it was in that
moment you became my darling.
Wow! Ha, ha!
Amazing!
Darling!
[ZERO TWO laughs]
[HIRO laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
[HIRO] The time I spend
laughing with you,
is filled with so much warmth.
And is so, so beautiful.
[KOKORO]
Mitsuru.
[MITSURU gasps]
[KOKORO]
Mitsuru?
Would you look at me, please?
I can't do that. Don't
ask the impossible!
[KOKORO]
Hm.
[MITSURU gasps]
Kokoro?
Together, let's find happiness.
Let's.
[IKUNO]
Mitsuru! Kokoro!
Now you look the part,
too, Mitsuru. Here.
--Thank you.
--Yeah, thanks, Ikuno.
[IKUNO chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
Hey, are we supposed to
be ringing the bells now?
Whatcha think?
Go for it!
[ALL laughing]
It feels like someone
should say something.
Like what?
[MIKU grunts]
I dunno, just something!
[ZOROME laughs] Look at him,
tryin' to act all cool.
Kokoro, though?
She looks beautiful.
[ALL cheering]
[computer beeps]
[HACHI] That reading...
An A.P.E Assult Ship?
Hey.
[gasps]
[HACHI]
What's the meaning of this?
Who authorized it?
Obviously Papa did.
Who else would?
[HACHI] Are you going to force
them into the parasite camp's
re-indoctrination program?
Squad 13's supposed
to be exempt from it.
Not all of them. Only two.
Which ones?
[9'a] You know what they
were up to, don't you?
So why don't you just
sit back and watch.
Just like you always do.
The couple will now
exchange the rings.
[grunts]
I'm sorry!
[KOKORO]
I'm okay. Keep going.
[MITSURU grunts]
[FUTOSHI]
Now...
Seal your vows with a kiss!
[FUTOSHI gasps]
[SOLDIER A] Everybody freeze!
You move, you die!
Who the hell are you?
Zorome!
[FUTOSHI grunts]
Run, you two!
Futoshi...! You guys!
[9'a]
There's nowhere for you to go.
You are trapped in
a birdcage, after all.
Why you-- What's the
meaning of this?
Papa's orders. He says the
two of you are dangerous.
[MITSURU gasps]
[9'a]
You need to be re-indoctrinated.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Still haven't given
up on playing human.
It's getting
embarrassing, really.
You're the one
who's embarrassing.
Ha! Think so?
[ZERO TWO grunting]
Zero Two!
[9'a] Now, now, you know that
you mustn't defy Papa's will.
Don't you, Iota?
Take them away.
[MITSURU, KOKORO gasp]
No! Let go! Mitsuru!
Get your hands off Kokoro!
Mitsuru!
[MITSURU grunts]
Kokoro...
[KOKORO]
Mitsuru. Mitsuru!
No! No! Let me go! Mitsuru!
[HIRO] Are we not allowed even
the slightest bit of happiness?
It's like nothing has changed
since we were in the Garden.
[HIRO] Where were Mitsuru
and Kokoro being taken?
Will they ever come back to us?
None of us had any answers.
And time passed mercilessly by.
If I were someone who
possessed emotions,
what sort of words could I
have said to the children?
As you are now,
maybe you could've
offered them support.
[MALE SAGE A] Do you mind
explaining to us what exactly
happened in the meeting
with the klaxosaur princess?
[MALE SAGE C] I thought
its purpose was to tell her
to surrender.
Why weren't we told they
would try to assassinate her?
[FEMALE SAGE A] We seek a
world where APE and humanity
can live for all eternity.
I thought we were working
as one to achieve that goal,
but perhaps I was mistaken.
[APE VICE CHIEF] What happened
was well within our predictions.
It won't be a problem.
We already possess
the replacement key.
[PAPA] You must look
at the big picture.
When we realize our ideals,
you will at last be freed from
the shackles of your shells.
Or as you call them, bodies.
[SAGES grunt]
[IKUNO] The parasites are
being summoned in order.
Where are they being taken?
Man, I don't like this place.
It reminds me of the Garden.
What I wanna know is how
long this will go on.
They said stand by
for our next mission.
Don't you remember?
But that was weeks ago, and we
still haven't heard anything!
[FUTOSHI] I just hope
Kokoro and Mitsuru are okay.
[beeping]
[ICHIGO gasps]
Guys, look!
[ALL gasp]
--[GIRLS] Kokoro!
--[BOYS] Mitsuru!
[ICHIGO]
Thank goodness.
We thought we'd
never see you again.
I'm so glad that
you're both okay!
Sorry! It was all my fault for
suggesting to do the wedding.
[MITSURU]
Wedding?
[HIRO gasps]
What is... a wedding?
C'mon! Don't you
remember the ceremony?
"Until death do us part,"
and all of that stuff.
You guys even exchanged
wedding rings.
Oh, this? I don't know
when it got there.
Anyway, who is she?
Did they give us
a new squadmate?
[KOKORO gasps] You're the one
who's new to our squad, not me.
[MIKU]
Hey, what's gotten into you two?
You're acting really weird!
Their memories
have been altered.
[HIRO gasps]
Just like ours, back then.
[HIRO]
The home we built for ourselves,
was too brittle to live in.
[HIRO]
Everything we ever hold dear,
is always destroyed in
the blink of an eye.
[KOKORO]
Huh?
Sakura?
[HIRO]
If that is our destiny,
then we can't let it
rule us anymore.
We're at the end of our rope.
♪