[007]
In the previous battle,
we successfully took
over the Gran Crevasse,
and the massive weapon
that lay underground.
Thus, "Star Entity" is now
completely under our control.
Tomorrow, we'll be
booting it up.
The FRANXX squads are tasked
with the following mission:
Keep all enemies away
from the weapon.
Many sacrifices will have
to be made. Do your best.
[MIKU]
Uh.
[007]
Huh? Yes, Code Three-Nine-Zero?
I'm sorry, but...
where'd Nana go?
Uh, what do you mean? I'm Nana.
Oh, right. I haven't
introduced myself yet.
I am Squad 13's new caretaker.
Code Zero-Zero-Seven.
[MIKU]
What? New caretaker?
And your code is...
So, um, this "Star Entity" is
a klaxosaur weapon, isn't it?
[007]
Right.
Are you sure...
this isn't risky?
[007 chuckles]
[MALE SAGE C] There's no need
to worry on that front.
[MALE SAGE A] That's why
we spent so much time
making modifications to it.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
Long story short,
we're implanting Strelizia
into Star Entity's core.
Doing this... will allow
us to control it.
[PAPA] Code Zero-Zero-Two,
we raised you with so much care,
all for this day.
We're counting on you.
Oh, yeah. Right.
Says the one who lied.
[HIRO] Assuming we do manage
to control Star Entity,
what happens after that?
If we exterminate
the klaxosaurs,
will we have a place
in that new future?
[PAPA] Of course. If we win this
war against the klaxosaurs,
the future will belong
to us, humanity.
[HIRO] Then this will be the
last time we call you Papa.
It's over.
We won't let you have control
of our destiny any longer.
♪
[HACHI] Doctor, we've received
word that Hringhorni
is ready for action.
[FRANXX]
I see.
A massive spear built
using klaxosaur cores.
Was such a thing
really necessary?
It's way too overboard.
More than anything,
it isn't beautiful.
Perhaps, but humanity
must need it to prevail.
[FRANXX]
How's Nana doing?
I had her brief Squad 13
regarding their up-coming
mission earlier, and--
[FRANXX]
Not that Nana.
Never mind. Do as you wish.
[GORO]
The rings?
This again?
Seriously, what?
[FUTOSHI] I'm saying,
look at them. Their hands.
See where their rings were?
They're gone.
I'm amazed you noticed that.
Wait, are you still
not over that.
Uh... Sorry.
[splashing]
Kokoro?
[IKUNO]
Hey, are you--?
[ICHIGO]
Kokoro!
[MIKU]
Ah! Wait!
[KOKORO gags, coughs]
[ICHIGO]
You okay?
It's happening a lot lately.
Maybe you should take
the upcoming mission off.
I'll be fine. Papa chose
to send me back here,
even after erasing my memories.
So... I must fight for him.
Even if it means
laying down my life.
[MIKU]
That's not true! You're wrong!
[KOKORO]
Huh?
You don't belong
to Papa, Kokoro!
And the same goes for
the rest of us, too!
[KOKORO]
Uh, but...
[MIKU] We must survive!
And leave a mark on the future!
You were the one who
taught us that!
I did?
[MALE SAGE A] APE has always
desired eternal peace
and prosperity for mankind.
[MALE SAGE E]
Soldiers! Fear not!
Offer up everything you
have in this mission.
[MALE SAGE C]
On this day,
we shall finally wipe
out the klaxosaurs,
and prevail in this war!
[9'e]
I can't say I approve.
Same. You guys stuck
out like a sore thumb.
You were an eyesore,
honestly.
[9'o] Yep. There you go again,
being so openly hostile.
You're like animals.
[ZERO TWO]
That's what you think.
But they are much stronger
than all of you are.
Their eyes are on the future.
Don't look down on humans.
[growls]
Don't get the wrong idea, Iota.
The only reason Papa gives
you guys special treatment
is because you're
tools for his plan.
You'll understand
in due time.
[ALL chuckle]
[alarm blaring]
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] Klaxosaur
pack currently at a distance
of 3,000. Heading fast
for the Gran Crevasse.
Multiple Gutenberg-class and
Lehmann-class identified.
[FEMALE OPERATOR B] Estimated to
reach first line of defense
in 103 minutes.
Considering we were
partners before,
we should be able to connect.
[laughs]
[MIKU shouts]
[IKUNO grunts]
[ICHIGO yells]
[KOKORO grunts]
[MITSURU] Okay. This might
actually work out.
Nice, Code Five-Fi--
Nice, Kokoro.
[grunts]
What was that?
[KOKORO]
What's wrong? Hey! Answer me!
[ICHIGO] Genista!
Don't stand still! Keep moving!
[KOKORO]
Hey. Come on! What should I do?
Answer me, Mitsuru!
KOKORO groans]
My-My head!
What's this pain? Is it
because I said her name?
[HIRO]
It sure is quiet.
[ZERO TWO]
Yeah.
[HIRO] Once we're done with
this, what do you wanna do?
[ZERO TWO]
I wanna go see the world.
You said you'd
show me, remember?
Where should we go? The ocean?
[ZERO TWO chuckles]
Then there's--
I don't care as long as
I'm with you, darling.
I just wanna travel the world.
Like that princess did.
[HIRO chuckles]
[ZERO TWO]
Hey, darling?
About the last page
of that picture book.
[HIRO]
Huh?
[ZERO TWO]
Uh. Never mind.
[HIRO]
Zero Two? I have a feeling...
...we're going to be put through
a trial by fire, but...
...it won't be our first.
We've gone through that before.
And each time, we found a
way to make things work.
Yeah. We'll be fine.
If we're together,
then we can defy any fate.
Together forever.
But, what if we're torn apart?
[HIRO]
I'll come get you.
[ZERO TWO]
Thanks. I'll get you, too.
[HIRO]
Promise?
[ZERO TWO]
Promise.
[FRANXX] Star Entity is ready
to go. Strelizia, move out.
[BOTH]
Roger that!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[HIRO]
What's wrong?
[ZERO TWO]
Something's... coming.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Unidentified flying object
approaching rapidly
from ten o'clock!
[PAPA]
Here they come.
[ICHIGO]
Genista!
[roaring]
[FEMALE FRANXX PILOT shouts]
What was that?
[ICHIGO]
What the...?
It's heading for
the Gran Crevasse!
[MALE FRANXX PILOT A screams]
[MALE FRANXX PILOT B]
No, this can't be!
[FRANXX] Guess they won't
make this easy for us.
What's that?
[HACHI]
I'll call for reinforcements.
[FRANXX]
They won't get here in time.
Prioritize the mission,
Strelizia!
Get going!
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO]
Uh, right!
Doctor, we should leave too.
[FRANXX grunts]
[001] Humans... You will not
do as you please with our child.
[FRANXX laughs]
[FRANXX] I see! So it is you,
Code Zero-Zero-One!
Princess of the Klaxosaurs!
[FRANXX]
It's been far too long.
Are you here to take
back Star Entity?
But, you can't operate it.
You don't have a partner.
You are the last
surviving klaxo-sapiens.
So, I'll operate it. Ever since
the day I first met you,
that's all I've dreamed of!
That's what all my
research has been for!
Princess! Sit there and watch--!
[FRANXX grunts]
[001]
You sinful man.
Doctor!
[001]
I...
[FRANXX groans]
[001]
...need no partner.
But, since I have the chance,
I shall use the one
you have provided.
[FRANXX]
What?
[HIRO]
No good. It's not gonna budge.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling.
This is Strelizia.
We've reached the entry point,
but the door won't open.
--[roaring]
--[ZERO TWO gasps]
They caught up?
We'll have to fight here!
Zero Two?
The controls.
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[grunts]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[HIRO]
What's going on?
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO groans]
Zero Two!
[001]
Ah, the fake the humans created.
A duplicate that does not
realize it is being used
by the invaders. You are
not fit to pilot our child.
[ZERP TWO]
What do you mean fake?
What are you talking about?
Zero Two! Zero Two!
[001]
Hm...
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[001]
I shall take him.
[HIRO gasps]
[gasps] Darling!
[grunts]
[HIRO grunts]
[001]
A curious taste.
You really must be
no ordinary human.
--Whaddayu--
--[001] Surrender yourself
to me.
Your body. Your soul.
I shall devour all that you are.
[HIRO gasps]
No...
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] Strelizia
has entered Star Entity.
[MALE SAGE C]
The worst has come to pass!
All the work put into Code Zero-
Zero-Two will have been in vain!
[MALE SAGE E]
Should the klaxosaur princess
connect to Star Entity,
our defeat is all but assured!
[APE VICE CHIEF] Worry not.
We've already taken measures.
[HACHI]
What is this?
She's connected...
with Strelizia?
[FRANXX gasps]
Doctor!
[FRANXX] I wasn't expecting
her to link with a human.
At this rate, she will
devour once again!
Tell me why. And how can you
be able to pilot Strelizia?
[001]
Of course I can.
This was originally
one of our brethren.
[HIRO]
Your brethren?
[HIRO grunts]
[HIRO]
What is this?
[ringing]
[ICHIGO]
What the...?
[MIKU]
It's a voice.
That's speaking...
[IKUNO]
...directly...
...to our brains.
[001]
Heed me, humans.
You ignorant fools who steal
the symbol of our bonds
that courses the
planet's depths.
"Courses the planet's depths"?
The magma energy.
[FRANXX] I found something while
studying klaxosaur corpses.
At some point in time,
their kind split,
becoming two different forms.
[FRANXX] One of which returned
to the earth and became energy.
[MALE SAGE A]
Steal? That's an affront!
[MALE SAGE C] Magma energy
is a planetary resource!
Its discovery saved human
civilization from certain ruin!
[001] Do you realize
how self-centered
a viewpoint that is? And now
you wish to steal my child?
I could never allow
that to pass.
For this child... is a
crystallization... of our bonds.
[9'a] Don't talk down to Papa,
you damn klaxosaur!
[HACHI] And... what
about the other form?
[FRANXX] It consumed that
energy and evolved physically.
[FRANXX]
It took an absurdly long time.
During which they stopped
mingling with one another,
and eventually lost
their intelligence.
Just what are the klaxosuars?
[FRANXX] Biological weapons
built by the klaxo-sapiens.
They are comprised of one male
and one female klaxo-sapiens.
The female's soul
connected to the weapon,
and the male's soul took root
in the core, the cockpit.
That sounds almost
like... a FRANXX.
[FRANXX]
Exactly.
They're merely an application
of the klaxosaur system.
Klaxosaurs that can
be piloted by humans
genetically modified
to be similar.
That... is what the FRANXX are.
So then... all this time
we've been piloting
klaxosaurs to fight klaxosaurs?
This isn't real.
I can't believe the klaxosaurs
have had pilots just like us!
[ZOROME gasps]
Could it be?
[MIKU]
The thing we saw. Back then!
[IKUNO] Yeah. Also...
remember the S-Planning?
[FUTOSHI] They were
excavating klaxosaurs...
...for the FRANXX.
They dug them up to serve
as the base of the units.
Damn it, no!
You've gotta be kidding!
What the hell is with that?
We've been kept in the
dark this entire time!
Where are we?
[001] Come. Awaken, my child.
They are nearly here.
Who are "they"?
[grunts]
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] Strelizia's
begun the implanting process.
[MALE SAGE C]
No.
[PAPA] I was hoping it
wouldn't come to this,
but we have no choice.
[MALE SAGE A]
What?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
We had wanted to take it
and Hringhorni into
space as soldiers.
[MALE SAGE C]
Into... space?
[PAPA]
If we can't have it,
then it can go down
along with this planet.
[MALE SAGE A]
What are you saying?
[PAPA] And we will return
to our "original roles."
[FUTOSHI]
An earthquake?!
[IKUNO gasps]
Look! Over there!
[GORO]
Are these...
[ICHIGO]
...some kind of klaxosaur?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[MIKU]
They can fly?!
[MIKU yelps]
[9'a]
Again?
[FEMALE FRANXX PILOT A]
An even bigger one!
[MALE FRANXX PILOT B]
What is this?
[IKUNO]
Klaxosaurs?
There's no way. This is
far too outrageous.
[ZOROME]
What the hell is this?
[FUTOSHI gasps] It's nothing
like our previous battles!
[ICHIGO] Just what in
the world is happening?
[ICHIGO gasps]
[HACHI] So, that's Star
Entity's awakened form?
[FRANXX]
This is it! My Strelizia Apus!
[FRANXX laughs]
Beautiful!
I wish I could have piloted it!
No, that doesn't matter anymore.
[HACHI gasps]
[001] Look at you. How ugly
the humans have made you.
But... you are still our child.
[001] A long time ago, when we
were attacked by invaders
from the expanse of space,
we fought and drove them off.
Then, we holed up in the earth,
and prepared for their return.
[HIRO]
"Invaders"?
[001]
Indeed.
[001] They are invaders.
Our true enemy. VIRM.
[HIRO]
True enemy? Invaders?
[001]
Filthy invaders.
This time. I shall not even
let you touch our planet.
[PAPA, SAGES gasp]
[001] Die. You will not...
take our planet!
[PAPA]
It's futile.
[001 gasps]
[ICHIGO gasps]
What happened?
[001 grunts]
Curse you, VIRM!
What did you do to our child?
[FRANXX gasps]
[FRANXX]
What? What's going on?
[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
This is VIRM's will.
[MALE SAGE C]
What?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
Star Entity is a mass of life
that could disturb
the universe's peace.
[PAPA] As such, if the klaxosaur
princess were to take over
the implanting process,
we programmed it to explode.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
The die has been cast.
[PAPA]
This planet...
[APE VICE CHIEF]
...will explode.
[PAPA, APE VICE CHIEF]
Leaving nothing behind.
Hiro. Zero Two!
[FRANXX]
Stop. Please stop!
Doctor!
[FRANXX] It's all ruined!
Apus, my ultimate work of works!
Don't defile it!
[APE VICE CHIEF] We will absorb
all lifeforms on this planet.
[PAPA] And will take you
to eternal paradise.
[001 grunts]
You impertinent fiends!
[HIRO yells]
Damn!
[HIRO gasps]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO]
I... I promised.
Darling. I'm gonna come get you.
[ZERO TWO]
No matter what!