[FRANXX] Of all the
heavy-handed measures to take.
[MALE SAGE E] We wanted to
eliminate all irregularities
before commencing this
important operation.
That is all.
[FRANXX]
If you keep doing this,
there's no guarantee that the
children will remain obedient.
[MALE SAGE C] Don't worry.
Nothing has happened to any
Squad 13 member aside
from those two.
[FRANXX]
But why?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
Since they're all together,
we decided it was best to
rid those parasites of all
unneeded emotions and
any related memories.
[FRANXX]
Why wasn't I consulted?
[PAPA] Werner, please just
behave for now.
You wanted to see this plan
come to fruition too, you know.
[FRANXX] They don't hesitate
to use forceful means
to achieve their ends.
But I'm no different.
♪
[door clatters]
[MAN A]
Uh, Werner?
Don't just walk in here!
[MAN A] The chancellor
asked me to get you.
[FRANXX]
APE?
[CHIEF]
Surely you have heard of them.
[sighs]
What does an upstart group such
as theirs want with me?
[CHIEF]
They say they want to hire you.
They are very impressed by the
research you've been doing.
Oh,  yeah?
[FRANXX scoffs]
They say which part?
[CHIEF] Ask them for the
details once you're there.
I accepted their offer.
You did?
That's right.
Without even asking me first?
You show absolutely no
sign of ceasing your
illegal experiments,
cloning chief among them.
The community is up in arms.
[FRANXX]
You call them illegal,
but the law only ever cracks
down after I'm finished.
The reason there's
no presumptive law against
what you're doing is because
no one expected a heathen
like you to show up
and start doing it.
Well, I am an atheist.
This is a matter of ethics.
You can't deny I'm
producing results.
No, that I cannot. I will
admit you're vastly talented.
But, honestly, I also
find you terrifying.
I'm "terrifying"?
[FRANXX] APE A mysterious
group of scientists
with no known origins
or nationalities.
An organization that operated
with the Lamarck Club
at its core.
They introduced revolutionary
mining technology
that could extract magma energy
from underground reserves
far deeper than man
had ever ventured,
creating a new, low-cost,
all-encompassing energy source.
With this energy revolution,
humanity drastically sped up
its progress toward the apex
of material civilization.
At the same time,
APE gained huge influence
in international politics
and the economy.
I don't mean to presume,
but you're Werner Frank,
aren't you?
Yes, I am.
I knew it! It's such
an honor to meet you!
[FRANXX]
Is it?
It is! I've read every single
one of your published
research papers!
Oh. I haven't introduced myself
have I? I'm Karina Milsa.
[FRANXX]
Hm...
Karina Milsa. Of regenerative
telomere medicine? That Karina?
Yup!
[gasps]
[APE VICE CHIEF] Do you have
a problem with the contract?
I don't.
I was just surprised by
the amount of funding.
[PAPA] It's simply a fair
valuation of your talents.
Well, to be honest,
I think you're expecting
too much from me.
This is somewhat outside
my field of expertise.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
With your abilities,
you should be able to
contribute more than enough.
Immortality. Magma energy can
even make that a reality.
Magma energy?
[FRANXX] It was more than
an ideal energy source.
They said it could even put
immortality within our reach.
Who would believe
such a tall tale?
But any scientist who said it
didn't pique their curiosity
would be lying.
[RESEARCHER A] We're not
seeing any indication of aging.
[KARINA]
Right.
I think we did it!
[MALE SAGE A]
So the research was a success?
[KARINA] I believe
that's a safe assumption.
Of course, we couldn't have done
it without Dr. Frank's help.
[KARINA] You don't seem
very happy about this.
Do I not?
Does something
about it bother you?
Just a guess, but in
exchange for immortality,
mankind might lose its
reproductive functions.
There's no evidence
indicating that.
No matter how we improve
ourselves with science,
we can't make up for
the inherent frailty
of our minds and bodies.
Above all, it strips
us of beauty.
Are you saying...
...it would be wrong for
mankind to attain immortality?
[FRANXX]
I wouldn't go that far.
I've wondered.
What's the pinnacle our
species can achieve,
our limit as organisms?
I might still find that answer
in our evolutionary process
post-immortality.
But what would we
be known as then?
Could we still
be called "human"?
[KARINA]
Do you mean we'd be gods?
[FRANXX chuckles]
I'm an atheist, you see.
[FRANXX] Not long after that,
it did indeed become clear
that the immortality
procedure led to the loss
of reproductive functions.
But many people still made the
choice to become immortal.
Around that time,
mankind recovered from its
rut thanks to magma energy
and quickly approached the
apex of material civilization.
But the only ones to benefit
from it were the rich,
with access to immortality.
The class divide
grew ever wider.
Some years later, to combat
the population explosion
resulting from immortality,
a law was passed in East Asia
heavily taxing childbirth.
It was the first step toward
mankind abandoning its
procreative instincts.
At the same time,
rapid desertification was
observed in the southern parts
of North America.
Some identified the mining of
magma energy as the cause.
But, naturally,
they were ignored.
I'm trying to tell you
how important this is!
Look, I feel bad for you,
but you're not going
to change my mind!
What were you talking about?
Oh, you saw that?
I'm sorry. I wasn't trying
to eavesdrop on you.
[KOKORO] For some reason
Futoshi doesn't want to be
my partner anymore. All he
says is he's going to team up
with Ikuno from now on, and he
wants me to ride with you.
But why is that?
It does seem really
sudden, doesn't it?
Everyone keeps
telling us stuff.
Abut all these things that
happened between you and me.
But we don't remember
any of it.
And even if they are
telling the truth,
the thought of me ever
developing those sorts of
feelings for you... is very
difficult for me to believe.
I know what you mean.
It's probably the same for me.
[FRANXX] At this point,
humanity's immortality rate
exceeded 70%.
And the rest was scheduled
to complete their procedures
within two years.
But as for me...
Still can't bring yourself
to undergo the procedure?
I don't like having
my body messed with.
If I was forced to,
I'd rather replace it
with a mechanical one.
Honestly, though. Don't you
think it's time you stopped
to consider your
life and the future?
Will you knock it off?
You know that's not my style.
Are you planning to
go under the knife?
No. I was hoping to
have a child, actually.
Oh?
[KARINA]
Is that surprising?
It's more that I was unaware
you had a partner, is all.
He can be pretty
dense sometimes,
so he hasn't noticed
my feelings yet.
Well, if you're that in
love with somebody,
you should ask him out to
dinner to try to clue him in.
[KARINA]
I did.
Oh, yeah? Then it sounds
like you did all you could.
Don't you think you're being
a little too dense right now?
Uh...
Then it's me?
[KARINA chuckles]
[FRANXX]
You have terrible taste.
But I guess I
don't mind. Much.
[FRANXX] By that time,
desertification had
become a global issue.
APE presented humanity's
ark to the nations of Earth.
The plantation project.
And essentially became
the leader of the world.
[FRANXX] That year, in front of
mankind, it made its appearance.
[FRANXX] Crying out as if
it were a newborn baby,
it destroyed the mining facility
and proceeded to make landfall.
It only stopped after being hit
by several nuclear
missile strikes.
As a result, the eastern half
of the Australian continent
became an exclusion zone.
Soon, these beings were
designated klaxosaurs,
or "screaming reptiles,"
and they began showing up
everywhere periodically.
It also became clear that
what they were attracted to
were the magma energy mines.
[FRANXX] The plantations
turned into mobile
anti-klaxosaur fortresses--
cities were abandoned,
and mankind disappeared
from the surface.
[KARINA]
Where are you going?
[FRANXX] Seems they've
secured a decently preserved
klaxosaur corpse in Alaska.
Okay. But we're supposed
to submit our marriage
registration next week.
Well, if I'm not back,
go submit it.
[FRANXX]
I was completely enthralled.
The body's composition
could be called both
mechanical and organic.
And it struck me as
profoundly beautiful.
Eventually, I noticed
it contained the same
X-X chromosomes seen
in female humans.
I didn't know
what that indicated,
but I had a bad
feeling about it.
My research was recognized, and
I was appointed lead developer
of an anti-klaxosaur weapon.
A robot called the FRANXX.
[FRANXX] Once FRANXX
development finally reached
the prototype stage,
it hit a prolonged roadblock
where it wouldn't start up.
After rigorous testing
under various conditions,
it was discovered
that the pilot needed
to still possess
reproductive functions.
You didn't have to volunteer
yourself to pilot.
You have a valuable test
subject right under your nose.
Don't you think it'd be
a waste not to use her?
I'm sorry.
Don't look at me like that. All
right, I'll see you in a bit.
--[alarm blaring]
--[FRANXX gasps]
[inaudible]
[FRANXX]
Is this a curse?
[FRANXX] The tests continued,
and many lives were sacrificed.
The pilots were put
under extreme stress.
But by injecting them
with yellow blood cells
that acted as a
conduit to the FRANXX,
and having them ride
in male-fepairs,
that stress was found
to be alleviated.
[FRANXX] After losing its
reproductive functions,
ironically, mankind found
a need for new children.
The FRANXX pilots, or parasites,
were therefore
called "children,"
and they were made to refer
to the rest of us as "adults."
[GORO] Those two didn't just
have their memories erased.
They also had elaborate
fake ones implanted.
Do you think their real
memories are lost forever?
[FUTOSHI]
This is messed up.
Was what they did really so bad
that they deserved to have
their memories erased like that?
Papa ordered it. I'm sure
that he had his reasons.
You serious, Zorome?
They destroyed everything
about the wedding
we worked so hard for!
Yeah, sure, maybe.
But we've only ever had
Papa our whole lives, so...
This isn't like you! I thought
you were better than that!
[ICHIGO]
Oh, Hiro. How's Zero Two?
She's all right,
but she still needs
to get some final tune-ups.
You guys. I'm thinking
of speaking to Papa.
I want to ask him to
return those two to normal.
Let's all tell him how we feel.
[ZOROME grunts]
[FRANXX] In the initial
usage phase of the FRANXX,
entire squads would die off,
taking the klaxosaurs
down with them.
But we pushed on and
succeeded in developing
more capable weapons.
After massive sacrifices,
we formulated an effective
means of killing them.
The Garden was
founded as a facility
to nurture the children.
And the plantations were fitted
with a quarantine zone
to house the parasites,
known as "Mistilteinn."
This is because the
parasites need emotions,
and we'd found
antiquated environments
were best suited
to raising them.
Their health is monitored
in extreme detail.
And everything is controlled
to keep them in the
best possible shape.
Eventually, the humans holed
up inside the plantations,
the "adults," forgot about
the existence of klaxosaurs,
and under the influence
of magma energy
and their immortality
treatments,
they obtained a life
of eternal tedium.
I was looking for
somewhere I belonged.
A resting place for my heart.
By this time, my interest in the
future of mankind had faded,
and I engrossed
myself in research,
seeking a more
perfected lifeform.
That's when a strange rumor
started making the rounds.
A rumor that said the
klaxosaurs had a leader,
a queen bee of sorts.
I don't know how,
but APE discovered where
that leader was hiding.
[PAPA] You may go along,
but on one condition.
Which is?
[PAPA] Should you encounter
the klaxosaur "queen,"
bring back something,
anything that could
serve as a DNA sample.
[FRANXX] Shockingly,
we found waiting for us
the remains of an unknown,
ancient civilization.
[001]
What are you doing here?
[SOLDIER A]
Who's there?
[001] Ignorant beings,
why are you here?
Why do you kill our brethren?
[SOLDIER A] What's this voice?
Where's it coming from?
Nowhere. It's transmitting
into our brains.
[SOLDIER B]
Klaxosaurs detected!
[SOLDIER A]
What? From which direction?
[SOLDIER B]
All of them!
[SOLDIER A]
We're surrounded.
Prepare for combat!
Form a perimeter circle!
[001] Your species is
so needlessly belligerent.
--[radar beeping]
--[SOLDIER A gasps]
[SOLDIER B]
Enemy rapidly approaching!
[MEN groaning]
[gasps]
[radar beeping]
[001] Don't kill that one.
Bring it to me.
[gasps]
[FRANXX]
I was exhilarated.
She was without a doubt
the most beautiful thing
I'd ever seen in my life.
[001]
Hold out your hand.
I smell my brethren on you.
It seems your sins
are far too grave
to be punished with mere death.
[gasps]
[001 growls]
[FRANXX screams]
[FRANXX]
Even as she bit off my arm,
I remained entranced
by klaxosaurs,
in love with their princess.
By that point,
I might have really already
lost all of my humanity.
[001] Begone! And tell your
kind to not lay a hand
on my brethren anymore.
[beep]
[FRANXX]
What is it?
[HIRO]
We have a request.
Mitsu-- Code Three-Two-Six
and Code Five-Five-Six.
Return their
memories to normal.
[PAPA]
That's impossible.
We didn't "seal off"
their memories.
We removed the
unnecessary information.
There's no way to
bring them back.
Oh, no...
[HIRO gasps]
[APE VICE CHIEF]
What you're currently doing
is a severe breach of protocol.
Ordinarily, you would
be punished,
but given your accomplishments,
we'll let you off with a mere
mention on your record.
Return to your waiting
quarters at once.
[gasps] Please wait. We--
[FUTOSHI]
Apologize! Apologize, damn it!
Futoshi?
How can act so carefree
after erasing...
Stop it! Don't get emotional!
[FUTOSHI] Don't try to
sweep this under the rug!
At least look a little sorry
for what you've done!
Would one damn apology kill you?
'Scuse me, but I was wondering
if you could tell us something
while we're here.
[PAPA]
What is it?
Would you please just tell us:
How many more klaxosaurs
do we have to kill
before we can finally
become adults?
All right. Then
what's the point?
What are we even living for?
Do we really only exist to
pilot the FRANXX and die?
You can at least tell
us that much, Papa!
Zorome.
You've taken from us. First Zero
Two's and my precious memories,
then Mitsuru's and Kokoro's.
We can't see you as
our Papa any longer.
Once this battle is over.
I want you to set us free!
[PAPA]
Very well.
As long as you fulfill your
duties in the next mission,
that is. We're done here.
[inaudible]
[FRANXX]
You rise up against fate.
Then show me... whether you
kids can be real humans or not.
[HIRO]
We'll decide our fate ourselves.
When I linked with Zero Two,
I saw you in her memories.
And I'll never forgive
you for what you did.
[ZERO TWO]
Darling, you pervert.
[HIRO chuckles]
[HIRO] Okay, Zero Two.
We've made our decision.
[ZERO TWO]
Mm.
[HIRO]
Ready? Let's go.
[FRANXX] Fate is cruel
more often than not.
But at times, it can be quite
powerless in the face of desire.
Zero Two, you would probably
hate me if you knew.
[FRANXX] Soon... Soon,
my dream will come true.
[FRANXX]
Show me your perfected form,
and how beautiful it can be.
♪