[ZOROME] I have the same
dream over and over again.
In it, for some reason,
I'm surrounded by darkness.
Staring at a distant
bright light and crying.
I dunno if these are
tears of sorrow or joy,
but they continue
to flow endlessly.
Gradually, the light grows
larger until it envelops me.
And I... let out a loud scream.
[ZOROME screams]
[MIKU]
Now!
[KOKORO shouts]
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
Now, Strelizia! End it!
Right!
[ZOROME]
Just sit back, Hiro.
It's my time to shine!
Here we go!
[roars]
[ZOROME]
See that? Piece-of-cake!
[MIKU] Hey, you better get
us out of here before it--
[MIKU shouts]
[MIKU gasps]
Nevermind.
♪
[MALE SAGE A]
Oh, my. How very intriguing.
[MALE SAGE C]
It's strange. Regardless of how,
they're linking in ways
other squads cannot.
[MALE SAGE B] Does this mean
the imbalances caused by
individualized FRANXX can
be an asset to the squad?
[FEMALE SAGE A] Any such benefit
is a doubled-edged sword.
The future we at APE exalt is
one of calmness and uniformity.
[MALE SAGE A] So you say they
are imperfect? How ironic.
[PAPA] I'm thinking it's
about time we move Squad 13
onto the next stage.
[SAGES]
Hm...
[MALE SAGE B]
To that area, you mean?
[APE VICE CHIEF] Recently,
we've detected klaxosaur
activity in the depths
of the Grand Crevasse.
It is Squad 13's duty to deliver
Code Zero-Zero-Two there
safe and sound.
[MALE SAGE A]
The plan is already in motion.
We must have them undergo
maintenance in the lab, at once.
[MALE SAGE D] Before that, why
don't we award them something?
[PAPA]
You mean, reward the children?
[MALE SAGE D]
Since ancient times,
awards have been the most
common way to inspire soldiers.
This may prove more effective
with them as their way of life
reflects a bygone era.
[PAPA] What an interesting idea.
I shall allow it.
[ZOROME]
Al lright! Can we drop this?
I apologized, didn't I?
You did not!
That wasn't an apology!
It didn't sound like your heart
was in it even a little bit!
They're still at it?
[ZOROME]
And how you can be so sure?
Can you read my mind?
Well, can you? Of course not!
Zero Two, you okay?
[ZERO TWO] I'm just...
thinking about something.
Apologize, now!
Over my dead body!
I swear, I'm gonna kill you
one of these days, Zorome!
[ZOROME] Ha! Let's see you try!
Come on! Come on!
You can't even touch me!
You can't-- Agh! Hey!
[MIKU]
I warned you!
Okay, kids! We need to talk!
I have good news!
Ahem. Tomorrow, you are all
to dress in your formal attire
and gather in the front of
the house at 0900 hours.
Understood?
Formal?
Is something happening?
[NANA] Papa values
what you've achieved
in battle thus far very highly.
As such, though there's
very little precedent,
he's decided to award
all of you with medals.
[MIKU, FUTOSHI gasp]
Wha--? Medals?
What're those?
The ceremony's tomorrow
at Plantation Parliament HQ.
You're serious, Nana?
Wait, then that means...!
Wow. We did it, Zorome.
Aren't you glad?
Uh. No, I'm lost.
You idiot, use your head!
She's telling us we're going
to be allowed into the city
for once!
[ZOROME]
Huh?! Really?
[gasps, shouts]
[ZOROME]
Yes! Hooray! I did it!
I don't think I've ever
seen him so happy before.
As he should be. This is what
Zorome's been working towards
for a long time!
[HIRO]
Huh?
[NANA]
Zero Two, wait.
Yeah, what?
The timing of this
is convenient.
I'll arrange for you to undergo
testing while we're in the city.
I hate those tests they give me.
I always feel lousy
after I take them.
And besides. I've been
doing great these days.
So I'll pass on the tests
for a while, thanks.
[NANA sighs] Here I thought Zero
Two had become a little more
obedient after teaming
up with a certain someone.
[HIRO gasps]
[GORO] We haven't worn these
since the welcoming ceremony.
Zorome, you're owning this
formal look. Very mature.
Heh. I know.
He'd better be after
he spent all morning
checking himself
out in the mirror!
[MITSURU]
To think,
he could've been looking
at something interesting.
Say what?!
[KOKORO giggles] But seriously,
you do look better than usual.
Ya got that right!
[MIKU]
Don't go flattering him, Kokoro.
Stuff like that goes
straight to boys' heads.
[ZOROME]
Shaddap!
[door clatters]
Good morning!
Is everyone ready to go?
[ALL]
Uh...
Come on. Hurry up.
[ZOROME shouts]
[ALL gasp]
Amazing!
[PLANTATION 13 MAYOR]
You are the first children
to ever be welcomed here.
This is a truly great honor.
I hope you consider this
day a source of pride
for a long time. Live up to this
honor bestowed upon you and
make even further contributions
to this plantation.
Are you the team leader?
Yes, sir! Code Zero-One-Five!
You have achieved great
things on the battlefield.
It speaks to your leadership.
Thank you for your kind words!
But those accomplishments
are not mine alone!
We all contribute!
Thank you for joining us.
It is an honor for Plantation
13 to host a former Nine.
And you've done well to live
up to the expectations
placed upon you.
[HIRO]
Uh, thank you, sir.
[PLANTATION 13 MAYOR] Thank you
for defending us adults.
Papa is overjoyed
by your success.
Your efforts have
been splendid, too.
Keep it up in the
battles to come.
[ZOROME gasps] I will!
Thank you very much, sir!
[HACHI] I'm going to visit
R&amp;D before I head back.
Take care of the children.
[NANA]
Got it.
[ZOROME]
Huh? That's all it was?
[NANA]
Well, yes.
It was over so quickly.
Aw, man. I was counting on there
being some kind of a feast.
I'm sure you'll live.
I know! Let's walk
back and see the city!
Great idea!
[ICHIGO gasps]
It wasn't that far.
We can walk back. Right, Nana?
[NANA sighs]
[NANA]
All right, let's go.
[ALL gasp]
[ZOROME gasps]
This is great. Someday I'll
live here, too, right?
After I get to become
an adult, of course.
Maybe. But, y'know,
for some reason,
I can't see us
becoming adults.
Same goes for me, actually.
There's no proof that
we'll be able to, anyway.
[ZOROME] That's because you
guys have no imagination at all.
[FUTOSHI]
"Imagination"?
With Zorome, it's delusion.
[MIKU giggles]
You can say that again!
Zero Two, d'you remember
a while back?
You once called
this city "lifeless."
What did you mean by that?
I meant exactly that.
You okay? You've been
acting kinda weird.
Did something happen?
I'm fine. I just couldn't care
less about this place, is all.
[MIKU giggles] I've never seen
it from so close before!
It's beautiful.
To think, that alone powers
the entire plantation.
Cool, huh, Ich--
[ICHIGO grunts]
I guess I shouldn't
have done that.
Huh? What are you talking about?
When I told you how I felt.
That was selfish of me to do.
So, please, don't let
it bother you.
[ICHIGO sighs]
All right, kids,
we're heading back now.
[KIDS]
Yes, ma'am!
[ZOROME]
Hup! Wha--!
[yelps]
[ZOROME]
Whoa! So cool!
[ZOROME gasps]
[ZOROME sighs]
[ZOROME]
What the--?
Seriously?
[ZOROME]
You're kidding me.
[ZOROME] Why isn't anybody here?
Are they all asleep?
[gasps] There's someone!
Hello! Excuse me!
They just ignored me?
[ZOROME grunts]
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A gasps]
[ZOROME shouts]
Oh, good.
You've finally woken up.
[BOTH gasp]
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
What a relief.
You didn't wake after I
initially treated you,
so I was a bit worried.
[ZOROME]
Uh. Oh. Thank you very much.
You're welcome. Of course,
your body and other things are
a little different from ours.
The medical checker just
wouldn't work on you.
But I kept trying and
eventually I thought to test
the other settings, such as
"pet mode," and success!
Am I... inside a
grown-up's house?
[ZOROME gasps]
Oh. Sorry about that.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A] My. That
must have been rough for you.
Yup. They're heartless,
that's all there is to it.
Don't you worry. I'll go send
word about this right away.
[ZOROME gasps]
Wait. Hold on.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Hm?
Before you make that call,
do you think maybe we
could talk for a bit?
Y'see. I've, uh, always
looked up to adults.
So I have a bunch of
questions and stuff.
Very well. I don't see any harm
in it. Let's have a little chat.
[ZOROME gasps]
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
But first, I'll make some tea.
[ZOROME grunts]
What are you doing?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Disinfecting.
Oh...
[ZOROME]
Mm?
Go on. Help yourself.
[gasps]
[ZOROME coughs]
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Did you enjoy the snack?
Heck yeah, it was super tasty!
Really? That's good to hear.
[ZOROME]
Aren't you gonna eat anything?
No, not me.
There was a time when I used
to enjoy the sense of taste,
but I don't really care now.
As long my body gets
the nutrition it needs,
I'm quite content.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Huh?
[ZOROME gasps]
Your home. It's pretty huge.
So how many people
live in this place?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Just two. My partner and myself.
That's it? Only two people
in this whole apartment?
That's correct.
[ZOROME] Wow. And adults
have partners, too, huh?
Oh, yes.
[ZOROME]
So, does that mean...? No, wait.
It's not because you
need to pilot a FRANXX.
So why do you have a partner?
Because we're following
a very old custom.
For the sake of convenience.
[ZOROME]
Custom?
A long time ago, men and
women used to pair up together
to form special
relationships, apparently.
They would do this to make
things easier and to procreate.
Life must've been uncomfortable.
[ZOROME]
Why's that?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Well, because they had to rely
on others for
every little thing.
Doesn't that sound
annoying to you?
[ZOROME]
I guess.
How would you like
to meet my partner?
[ZOROME]
What? Is he here?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A sighs]
Come with me.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
This man is my partner.
Oh.
That's a big smile on his face.
Whatever he's dreaming about,
it must be amazing.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A chuckles]
[ZOROME gasps]
He's not dreaming at all.
He's receiving his
dose of happiness.
[ZOROME]
Huh?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A] You see,
he's activating his brain's
reward system to gain
a sense of pleasure.
A truly, truly wonderful thing.
[ZOROME]
Hm.
I'd rather get it from eating
more of those snacks you had.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A grunts]
[ZOROME gasps]
Hey, are you okay?
I'm just feeling a bit tired.
Let's go back to
the living room.
[ZOROME]
Uh, sure.
Are you really all right?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A] I'm sorry.
It's been such a long time
since I've talked with someone
this much. I'm not used to it.
For real? But don't you and your
partner talk to each other?
We don't. Come to think of it,
I can't remember his voice.
[ZOROME]
You haven't spoken in that long?
There's no need for us to speak.
[ZOROME]
Are you guys on bad terms?
Oh, no.
I don't think either of us is
dissatisfied with our partner.
We don't meddle in
each other's business,
which gives us the freedom to
live our lives as we please.
I guess that
sorta makes sense.
Honestly, I can't even tell
you how much I have to hear
my partner's voice
each and every day.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Oh?
Of all the girls in our squad, I
got partnered with the loudest,
naggiest one!
Talk about bad luck!
She gets so emotional!
We break into these big
arguments at the drop of a hat!
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Sounds like you got matched
with the wrong person, then.
You should change your partner.
[ZOROME gasps]
If there's a problem
between you two,
doesn't it negatively
impact your missions?
Uh. Maybe. I guess. But the
truth is, it doesn't really
bother me when the
two of us are fighting.
And I'm probably the only
one who can deal with how
cranky she is. At least, I don't
think the other guys can.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Well, if there isn't a problem,
then I guess it's fine.
There's no problem
at all. Even Miku--
Oh. I forgot to tell you, that's
my partner's name. Miku.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Her name?
[ZOROME] Yeah, our squad has
these nicknames for each other.
Everyone calls me Zorome,
but my code number is--
Six-Six-Six.
[ZOROME]
Oh. I must've told you that.
Anyway! When it comes to Miku,
she has an awful personality,
but her looks aren't half-bad.
And, to be honest,
she is pretty cute, when she
keeps her mouth shut.
Sometimes, when we're
fighting klaxosaurs and stuff,
I get this really strong
urge to protect her,
and take care of her,
as weird as that sounds.
It makes me wonder, maybe
that feeling's what lets us
fight together. Oh, wow.
Is that why FRANXX are
built to be operated by
male-female pairings?
[gasps] Are you all right?
I'm fine. Don't worry.
However, I've grown
quite tired now,
so I'll send word for
someone to pick you up.
[ZOROME] Oh. Okay.
It's getting late, anyway.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Yes. I checked with him.
There's no doubt about it.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A] They say
they'll be here, right away.
[ZOROME]
Thanks for all your help.
Is something wrong?
[gasps]
Uh, nothing.
Are you still in pain somewhere?
Oh. No. I'm okay.
But then why...?
I don't know.
You sure?
Not really. I'm confused.
Even though this is the
first time I've met you,
I don't know why, but you
feel really familiar to me.
And I...
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
What makes you feel that way?
[ZOROME]
I don't know.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
In my case,
I believe this is the first
time I've really met you.
You're right, it is.
It's just... it feels like...
How do I say this?
You know, it feels like...
...someone's always been
watching over me.
Gentle and kind, and always
there to protect me.
Well, then.
You're quite mistaken.
[ZOROME]
Huh?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Because I cannot protect you.
[ZOROME]
Huh?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
On the contrary,
you children are the ones who
are busy protecting all of us.
[ZOROME gasps]
Yeah, that's true.
Yes, it is. You protect
this entire plantation.
[ZOROME]
Yeah.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
That's something to be proud of.
And I'll keep protecting it.
I won't be defeated.
I'll fight and fight and fight
and kill every klaxosaur!
Then after that, one day,
I'll become an adult, too.
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
Huh?
When I do and I'm finally
allowed to live in this city.
Would you be,
well, uh, my fami--?
I mean, would you be my friend?
No, that is obviously
out of the question.
[ZOROME]
It is?
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
After all, you are--
[doorbell buzzes]
[MYSTERIOUS WOMAN A]
I treated his wounds.
And I fed him a little,
but that was about it.
[MALE MEDIC A]
Don't make us waste our time.
This isn't a place infected
children like you should enter.
[MALE MEDIC B]
Cut it out.
They're basically victims
in all this, too.
The poor, pitiful things.
[ZOROME grunts]
[MALE MEDIC B]
Hm?
[ICHIGO]
Good news! They found Zorome!
[ALL gasp]
That jerk. Making us
all worry like this!
I sentence him to one week
of cleaning the bathroom!
[ZOROME] It's not true.
We're not pitiful.
[whistles]
Stop that! You're supposed
to take this seriously!
[ZOROME] I am! What are
you keeping watch for?
It's not a show!
[ZOROME] Why did that adult
woman feel so familiar to me?
I thought about it a bunch
of times after that day.
But in the end,
I never found an answer.
Eventually, I stopped
thinking about it.
I even forgot about her.
And ever since, I stopped
having that dream.
♪