[arlams blaring]
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Plantation 13 will now commence
the kissing with Plantation 26.
[HIRO]
The first time that we met,
Zero Two told me that a
kiss was "a special thing."
I wonder, do the adults kiss?
And if so, who was it that first
likened the act of plantations
making contact to a kiss?
Question. What exactly is this
"kissing" thing, anyway?
You've watched this whole time
and you're still clueless?
Shut up! Dumbass. If you
know so much, explain it!
[MIKU gasps] Well, it's when two
plantations are stuck together.
Yes, but that's not all.
True. There's also the
transfer of magma fuel
between the plantations.
Through that big pipe there.
And that fuel's essential.
Both for the adults' survival,
as well as our own.
Not to mention,
FRANXX need it to operate.
[ZOROME] Oh, so we
can relax now, right?
Well, not exactly.
It's a large-scale transfer
of magma energy.
Which means it could attract a
massive number of klaxosaurs.
Seriously?
Massive? That's great.
Don't worry, guys.
[OTHERS]
Huh?
As long as we work
together, we'll be fine.
Especially now that we have
Strelizia on our team.
But, Hiro.
[ICHIGO]
Yeah. Hiro is right about that.
[HIRO] They held a grand
ceremony to mark the occasion.
A solemn affair.
The children from
Plantation 26's FRANXX squad
were there, too, of course.
Though, they all seemed
to be a lot calmer
and more composed than we were.
[SQUAD 26 HEAD A]
Boys and girls!
The dreaded klaxosaurs
are certain to attack
our magma reserves
in great numbers.
The fate of these
two plantations
rests squarely on
your shoulders.
But we believe that you
are up to the challenge.
You are strong, and you will
surely bring us victory!
[HIRO] Being treated like VIPs
gave our morale a big boost.
[HIRO] But at the same time,
we sensed the coming of a battle
fiercer than any that we had
ever experienced before.
♪
[GORO yawns]
'Kay, Hiro. Wake up time.
[GORO] Hm. Rise and
shine, sleepy-head.
[GORO gasps]
[GORO] Are you okay? Your body
was burning up back there.
[HIRO]
I'm perfectly fine.
If anything, I feel
light on my feet today.
You're not lying, are you?
Of course not.
In fact, I'm eager to get out
there and do some training
right now.
Okay, then.
[KOKORO] Yesterday's ceremony
was something, huh?
I was so excited
that I had trouble
falling asleep last night.
[MIKU] Plantation 26's squad
leader seemed like a nice guy.
Is he the kind of person
you'd wanna ride with?
Better him than any of
the boys we're stuck with.
Wouldn't you agree?
Not really.
I couldn't care less.
What a wet blanket.
It sure gives you a
confidence boost
when the adults have
faith in you, huh?
Yeah. Plus, It shows
how much they need us.
"But, we believe you are
up to the challenge!
You are strong, and you will
surely bring us victory!"
[ALL laugh]
[ZOROME]
And as the strongest,
I'll be the one who leads
us to that victory!
I think you mean Hiro will
be the one to lead us.
[gasps]
That's right.
You really excelled
in that last battle.
We'd've been lost without
you saving the day.
But how are you feeling?
Is everything okay?
[HIRO]
As a matter of fact, yeah.
Everything's fine.
Good to hear!
Looks like that whole
"three times and you die"
rumor was a bunch
of nonsense, then.
Either that, or he's just
extremely compatible
with the girl.
[HIRO]
Thanks, guys.
Although, it took all of
us to win that battle.
I had trouble keeping up at
times, but it all felt so right.
As long as I can keep riding,
then I hope you'll let me fight
with you as part of the team.
[ZOROME]
Ha! Don't get cocky, man.
I mean, all you did was
get through one time.
[GORO] Do you always
have to be such a downer?
[HIRO]
Zorome?
What?
I'll try hard not
to be a burden.
So whadda ya say?
Let's fight together.
Uh... Well, uh...
Fine, if you're gonna
make a big scene.
Just try to keep up
with me, all right?
[MIKU]
Big words, little man.
[ZOROME] Oh, shut up!
It's just, you know,
as the team's ace pilot,
I feel it's my duty to
maintain a certain sort of...
'Kay, we get it.
[clock chimes]
[FUTOSHI] Breakfast time!
♪ Breakfast, breakfast.. ♪
[ICHIGO]
Hiro, hang on a sec.
[HIRO]
Mm?
[HIRO gasps]
[ICHIGO gasps]
Your collar was
bent out of shape.
You really need to learn
to take better care
of these sorts of things.
[HIRO grunts]
[ICHIGO] By the way, I was
amazed you were able to
figure out what I was going
for in that last battle.
[HIRO]
Well, I have known you forever.
Which is also why I
was always confident
that you would
work something out.
[HIRO]
Glad you trust me so much.
But don't think for a second
that I wouldn't have
chewed you out if
you'd messed up.
[HIRO laughs] Wow, you're
such a hard-ass.
Anyway, I wanted
to say, back then--
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Good morning, darling!
[HIRO]
Oh, good morning.
[ZERO TWO giggles]
This way.
[HIRO]
Uh, hey, wait.
[ZOROME yelps] You can't
sit there, you're a girl!
Yeah, and that's my chair, so--
Go sit at the girls'
table where you belong!
[ICHIGO]
Pipe down.
It's time for us to pray,
so all of you be seated.
[FUTOSHI]
B-But, my seat is, um...
Would you like to sit
here next to me, Futoshi?
What? Can I, really?
[ZOROME]
Huh?!
[ICHIGO]
May Papa never thirst.
May Papa's heart be filled
with peace for all eternity.
Now let us eat.
[ALL]
[ZERO TWO]
Here you go, darling.
Say, "Ahh."
[HIRO grunts]
Ahh...
[ZERO TWO]
Good?
[HIRO]
Yeah, it is.
[ZERO TWO] You can
eat the rest of mine.
Lucky jerk.
I wanna have somebody
feeding me like that, too.
Well, then why not ask your
partner to feed you?
Ha! I'd rather get a cute
girl like Kokoro do it,
but she would nev-- Agh!
[KOKORO giggles]
We see, we do.
Sheesh. Why are you all
so easily influenced?
[ZOROME yelps]
One more time. Open!
[HIRO] Over here, we have
fixed times for waking up,
bathing, going to sleep.
It's all according to schedule.
Everything's laid out for us,
right down to the clothes we
wear and the food we eat.
[ZERO TWO]
Hm...
[HIRO] This entire forest
was designed to fine-tune
the parasites' numbers,
apparently.
[ZERO TWO] Is that why
there's a ceiling over it?
[HIRO]
Prob'ly.
But, even with the ceiling,
it's not like it doesn't rain.
Wait, "rain"?
[HIRO] Mm-hm. Water comes
pouring down from up there.
Oh, I wanna see that!
Make it rain!
[HIRO gasps]
I wish I could,
but Papa and the others
decide when it happens.
Show me. Right now. Just do it.
[HIRO]
Mm. I can't.
[ZERO TWO sighs]
[HIRO] So, hey. Why the
sudden interest in having me
show you around this place?
[ZERO TWO]
Huh? Why?
Because I'm gonna be
living here now, too.
[HIRO gasps]
[GORO gasps]
Huh?! What is a girl
doing in here?
This is the boys' wing!
Get her outta here this instant!
[HIRO]
Sorry! My mistake! We'll leave!
C'mon, Zero Two, let's go.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
Good grief. Look at them,
holding hands.
[NANA] Zero Two is going to
remain here for a while.
Papa gave her his permission.
Does that mean Hiro's
an official parasite now?
At the moment, that's
still under consideration.
But I'm assuming
it'll happen.
Ichigo. Make Zero
Two feel at home.
[GORO]
What do you think?
[ICHIGO]
About what?
[GORO]
How Hiro's acting.
[ICHIGO]
Well, it's been a long time
since I've seen him
smile so much.
[GORO]
Yeah.
But what if he was forcing
himself to be all cheery?
[ICHIGO]
Did he say something?
[GORO] No. You know he wouldn't
just tell us straight out.
But, you could ask--
--[ICHIGO] Goro.
--[GORO gasps]
[elevator chimes]
I know you're
worried about Hiro,
and that's fine, but we have to
look out for ourselves, too.
What's that supposed to mean?
This upcoming battle
will be worse
than any we've experienced.
You're my partner, which means
that if you're not a hundred
percent focused, then I
can't do my best, either.
Why me, and not him?
[coughs]
What's the difference
between Hiro and me?
--[door clatters]
--[MITSURU gasp]
Mitsuru?
Yeah, what is it?
Oh. I saw you come in here,
so I followed you.
Are you all right?
Seems like something's
been bothering you recently.
Yeah, I'm fine. Don't worry.
If you'd like, I'd be willing
to help you any way I can.
You're so tough.
You never rely on anyone--
[MITSURU]
Are you pitying me?
[KOKORO gasps]
I-I didn't mean to.
[MITSURU]
Leave me alone.
This is going to be your
room for the time being.
I'd much rather be
with my darling.
[ICHIGO] You're going to live
here for a while, right?
Then you'll have to
follow our rules.
Don't expect any
special treatment.
Also, you'd better take
good care of Hiro.
[ZERO TWO] I don't need
you to tell me that.
My darling belongs to me.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro doesn't belong to anyone.
You're pretty bossy, aren't you?
[ICHIGO]
Thanks for the compliment.
[HIRO gasps]
[ZOROME]
Hey! Goro!
[CODE 090]
Interesting.
Your FRANXX all
have unique designs.
[GORO]
What are you talking about?
[IKUNO] Yeah, we thought
that was standard.
[CODE 090]
Course not.
Our FRANXX have similar
bodies and equipment.
That makes it easier for all of
us to fight as a cohesive team.
[FUTOSHI]
Huh.
[CODE 090] They've told us
that you were a rather
hastily-assembled test team,
so does that mean this
is your first encounter
with kissing then?
[GORO]
Yeah.
[CODE 090]
I see.
Then we're vastly more
experienced than you.
So if there's anything you
don't understand, just ask us.
[ZOROME]
Ooh! Ooh. Me, me! Yeah!
I've got a question for you!
Have any of the children
from your squad
gone on to become adults?
"Become adults"?
Prob'ly doesn't know.
[CODE 090]
Ah, that's what you mean.
Not from our squad, no.
Oh. Well, have you at least
heard any rumors about it?
[CODE 090]
No, sorry.
What the heck?
[FUTOSHI] You really care
about that, huh, Zorome?
[ZOROME] Because I'm not a
simpleton like you, Futoshi!
[CODE 090]
How peculiar.
I mean your nicknames.
It was Code Zero-One-Six
who started coming up
with them, correct?
[GORO]
Hold on. You've heard of Hiro?
Yes. Everyone has. That guy
is famous amongst us children.
You guys truly are unusual.
FRANXX designs all
over the place.
Using nicknames instead
of code numbers.
What's the point
of that, by the way?
[GORO gasps]
[HIRO grunts]
[GORO]
Hiro!
[NANA] What's going
on with these abnormal
yellow blood cell counts?
I'm amazed he's still alive.
It's the polar opposite
of the reaction
the other parasites had
after riding with Zero Two.
It would be dangerous to
let him ride with her again
when we don't yet
know the cause.
Maybe, but we'll need Strelizia
in the upcoming battle
if we want to win.
The next one will
be his third time.
[GORO] Hey, Hiro!
What's wrong with you?
[HIRO grunts]
It's nothing.
Yeah, right! Nothing,
my ass! Are you injured?
[GORO gasps]
[HIRO grunts]
[GORO]
How long has that been there?
Since you rode with Zero Two?
[GORO grunts]
Hey!
[HIRO coughs]
Don't pilot Strelizia again.
[HIRO]
That's not your call.
You do know the next time
could kill you, right?
I do. And yet, in this moment,
I feel so very alive.
[GORO gasps]
I haven't felt this way
in such a long time.
I wanna give it my all
on this upcoming mission.
I don't want things to end
in failure, so please, ju--
You want me to turn a blind eye?
[HIRO]
That's right.
And the others. You wanna
keep this from them?
That's right.
Even Ichigo?
[grunts] You can't!
I'm sorry.
You are such a complete
and utter fool.
[HACHI] An hour ago,
we detected klaxosaurs
at a distance of
approximately 3,000.
There are anywhere
between a hundred
and a hundred-fifty of them.
A hundred-fifty!
[HACHI] That number is
expected to climb even higher.
Meanwhile, their ETA is
about 33 hours from now.
No matter how much
we try to rush it,
there's no way we can
complete the kissing process
before they arrive.
So we're going to position
a line of defense here,
with Squad 26 at the vanguard.
Behind them, Squad 13 will
stand by, serving as backup.
Wait. Why are we the backup?
[CODE 090] This is gonna
be a chaotic dogfight.
Our squad can link up better
if we go at it by ourselves.
[ZOROME gasps]
Did he just call us deadweight?
'Cause it sounded like it.
[HACHI] Ahem. Defending the
main pipe that links
the two plantations together
must be our top priority.
Which is why I've decided
to deploy a single FRANXX
capable of solo combat
there to guard it.
[CODE 090] But what
FRANXX is up to that task?
You may know it as Strelizia.
[GORO grunts]
[ALL gasp]
Did you say... Strelitzia?
No way... You can't mean.
Excuse us. Sorry we're late.
[CODE 090]
Code Zero-Zero-Two!
[HACHI]
Did Papa approve?
Yes, we're a go.
Hiro will pilot Strelizia as
Zero Two's partner once again.
[HACHI] This is our best
course of action right now.
Got it.
[CODE 090]
Hold on. We can't do it.
We will not fight
alongside Strelizia.
[HACHI]
The plan is final.
But, sir.
That girl doesn't care about
her allies in the slightest!
We can't trust her to have
our backs in the field!
Code Zero-Zero-Two has proven
that fact in the past.
What're you saying?
[CODE 090] The joint
operation two years ago!
When your reckless and utterly
selfish fighting style wound up
leaving us isolated out
there on the battleground,
and I lost my partner!
[CODE 090 breathes heavily]
Too bad. Doesn't ring any bells.
Weaklings die all the time.
Big deal. It happens.
[CODE 090 gasps]
Stop. I'll watch Zero Two
and keep her under control.
As Strelizia's stamen,
you have my word.
[ZOROME] Where does that
guy get off treating us like
we'd be in the way?
[MITSURU] He may not be wrong.
We are a makeshift team.
[IKUNO] But it still pisses
you off, doesn't it?
[GORO] I agree with them.
With Squad 26.
[ZOROME]
Huh?
Strelizia shouldn't be getting
anywhere near this mission,
--[HIRO] I've got this.
--let alo--
Come on, let's show them
what we're made of!
You guys don't wanna just take
their insults lying down, right?
Uh. No! He's right, Goro.
So don't start
wussin' out on us.
[GORO]
What do you think, Ichigo?
I think that we need Strelizia.
[GORO gasps]
[HIRO groans]
[GORO grunts]
[GORO gasps]
Where're they goin'?
[ICHIGO] I'm not going to say
anything about your history
with Squad 26.
[ICHIGO] However, I need you to
stay in line during the mission.
I'm the leader here,
and you will follow my orders.
Telling me what
to do again, huh?
You really are bossy.
Hey. Wait!
I'm not done talking--
[ZERO TWO]
What?
[ICHIGO] Please, don't push
Hiro too hard.
Don't forget, my darling said
he wanted to ride with me.
[ICHIGO]
I know that.
But can you at least try to not
put such a heavy burden on him?
[ZERO TWO] Do you want
me to give him to you?
[ICHIGO gasps]
You already tried
riding with him,
and it didn't work, remember?
[ICHIGO]
You leave me out of this!
Then stop putting
yourself into this.
[ICHIGO gasps] Are you
trying to suck Hiro dry?
My darling belongs to me.
[ICHIGO gasps] He could
die out there, you know!
If he does, then he
didn't amount to much.
[ICHIGO gasps]
You're heartless!
What they said is true!
You aren't human!
[ZERO TWO]
Human? Human, you say?
Let me ask you something, then.
What is "human" to you people?
Tell me that.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[GORO]
You'll catch a cold.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[ICHIGO] Thanks. I had to
take care of something.
Yeah.
[ICHIGO]
Did you see the whole thing?
Uh, yeah.
[ICHIGO] I don't know
what to do. Not anymore.
I'm supposed to be the leader,
and he and I go way back.
But I couldn't help Hiro pilot.
I couldn't...
I couldn't stop him.
But she's there for him now,
and that's what Hiro wants.
But I... I...
Something is wrong with me.
Ichigo?
[ICHIGO whimpers]
I... I hate this!
I can't stand it. My mind's
a mess. What's going on?
But... Hiro...
[GORO gasps] Ichi--
What's this feeling?
[whimpers]
[footsteps]
[ZERO TWO] Everything smells
nice after it rains.
Make it rain again soon.
Oh, right, I forgot.
You can't make it rain, huh?
We don't know that. Not yet.
[HIRO]
Hm?
[ZERO TWO] This is where
we first met. Remember?
[HIRO]
It's only because I met you
that I'm standing
here right now.
That I can pilot a FRANXX.
[ZERO TWO]
That's right.
Your partner is me,
and me alone.
You already know
about it, don't you?
How in the past, none of my
partners have ever been able
to ride with me more
than three times?
Yeah.
[ZERO TWO] It hurts, right?
Unbearably so?
But, it looks beautiful.
Last chance. If you want
off this ride, say it.
I am your partner.
[ZERO TWO giggles]
[HIRO] Even if these
wings I reached out
and grabbed are to snap one day.
I'll still take
flight into the sky.
Because. I feel that's
why I'm here right now.
♪