[ZERO TWO] The Jyan, also known
as "the bird that shares wings,"
only possesses one wing.
[ZERO TWO] Unless a male and
female pair lean on each other
and act as one,
they're incapable of flight.
They're imperfect,
incomplete creatures.
[ZERO TWO sighs]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
But, for some reason...
[ZERO TWO] ...their way
of life... struck me as...
...profoundly beautiful.
It was beautiful, I felt.
[ZERO TWO]
I wanna take a bath.
[FRANXX] Not again.
Show some self-restraint.
[sniffs] Hey, how do I smell?
[FRANXX]
Let the man rest.
That last battle
took a lot out of him.
My goodness, why must she always
be such high maintenance?
[ZERO TWO] Does Plantation
13 have an ocean?
[NANA]
Why do you ask?
[ZERO TWO] I wanna swim
in some clear ocean water.
[NANA] I'm sorry to tell you
there's no ocean down there.
Can't you just take a shower?
[ZERO TWO]
I'm in the mood for a swim.
[MALE PILOT A] We'll be
starting our descent soon.
Please take your
seats and buckle up.
[NANA]
You got it. Save that thought.
Ugh, I really hate how I taste.
[HIRO] The Jian is also known
as "the bird that shares wings."
I read a book about them a long
time ago that said they can't
even fly unless a male and a
female support each other.
They're pitiful creatures.
[HIRO]
Until one finds a partner,
it must hide amongst
the tree leaves.
Waiting with baited breath.
Dreaming of the day when
it can finally take flight
into the skies above.
[thud]
Blood.
[chirping]
[gasps]
[HIRO]
Hey, wait.
[HIRO] So then where does a bird
that ends up never flying go?
[gasps]
[HIRO] I know the answer
to that all too well.
[HIRO]
The answer is...
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Found one.
[FUTOSHI]
"Partner Killer"?
[ZOROME]
That's right.
Apparently, the girl
has horns and fangs.
They say that after the third
time any parasite rides
with her, he has his blood
sucked out and winds up dead,
without fail.
[FUTOSHI] Ugh. I don't
wanna ride with her.
[MIKU] Oh, come on.
That's just a rumor, isn't it?
[ZOROME]
It's 100 percent true!
I know somebody who
actually overheard security
talking about it.
[GORO]
Ichigo. Any word from Hiro?
[ICHIGO]
No, not yet.
[ZOROME]
Speaking of...
Is he really gonna stick
around here after all?
Well, he didn't show up
at today's briefing,
for whatever that's worth.
It could mean he's
turning down the offer.
Hiro's leaving?
But that'll be so sad.
If he does quit,
where does that leave Naomi,
who was also caught
up in his issues?
[MITSURU] I say he's showing
some real integrity.
Besides, it's gotta be hard
for him to face us all
after what happened.
Try putting yourselves in
his shoes for a change.
Gimme a break.
You all right, Ichigo?
He's such an idiot!
[FRANXX] Good grief.
These transport planes' seats
are too rugged for
an old man like me.
Can't we find some
other means of travel?
[NANA] You'll just
have to deal with it.
We don't have many
options when it comes to
transporting cargo of this size.
[FRANXX]
I haven't seen you in ages,
but it seems you're
still as stiff as ever.
Wish the seats
and your personality
could be this soft and yielding.
Knock it off, Doctor!
[FRANXX]
How's Hachi doing?
[NANA] He's been asked to speed
up the children's training.
After all, this will be
our first trial run
for the unit we're
using this time.
[FRANXX]
I see.
Doctor, may I ask you something?
Why run the test case
here of all places?
And with such a
makeshift team, no less?
[FRANXX]
Something's been bothering me.
The geezers in APE
might not understand it,
but it troubles me nonetheless.
So you do have some
sort of idea in mind.
Oh, and while I'm
thinking about it,
please do attend the
startup ritual, Doctor.
[FRANXX]
Yes, I know. By the way,
I see that our little problem
child has already gone missing.
[NANA gasps]
She was here just a second ago.
[FRANXX]
Look there.
[NANA gasps]
Damn! Always running off.
[footsteps]
[chirping]
[gasps] It's still alive!
[HIRO] I never knew there
was a place like this here.
[HIRO]
A parasite?
But that uniform doesn't
look like ours at all.
[splashing]
[HIRO grunts]
[gasps]
[gasps, grunts]
[gasps] Oh, no! She's drowning!
I've gotta help her!
[HIRO yelps]
[HIRO] It was like I'd
been put under a spell.
Between those two
alluring horns,
and my first-ever glimpse
of a naked girl's body,
I was transfixed, unable to
take my eyes off her.
[HIRO gasps] You're... You're...
You're naked! I'm sorry!
Wow. And here I thought
you were dead.
Hey, are you a parasite?
And what were you doing
bathing out here?
[ZERO TWO]
It's weird.
I thought ocean water was
supposed to be salty.
Uh, this isn't an ocean.
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
But this puddle's the closest
thing I could find to an ocean
around these parts,
so here we are.
Well, aren't you gonna swim?
[HIRO]
Uh? Me? No, I'm good.
Really? But it feels so nice.
And the way you were staring,
I thought you wanted
to take a dip, too.
[HIRO]
I wasn't staring.
I was worried that you were
drowning out there, okay?
I jumped in to save you and--
[gasps]
Uh, would you mind, y'know,
putting clothes on?
[ZERO TWO] Hm. I get it!
You're some kind of pervert!
[gasps] What, why?
[HIRO yelps]
It's not what it looks like!
[giggles]
You should see your face!
[ZERO TWO giggling]
[ZERO TWO]
But, hey.
You really jumped in
to save me, didn't you?
I appreciate it. So thank you.
[ZERO TWO] That uniform.
Are you a parasite, too?
[HIRO]
No.
[ZERO TWO]
So you don't pilot?
[HIRO] I can't pilot.
I no longer have the ability.
Worse, I dragged my
partner down with me.
[HIRO] I don't have
a place here anymore.
[ZERO TWO]
Huh. So you're just like me.
[HIRO grunts]
I'm always alone, too,
thanks to these horns.
If you don't belong here,
build a place where you do.
If you don't have
a partner, find one.
And if you can't, take one!
[HIRO gasps]
[ZERO TWO] Mm, your taste
makes my heart race.
It has a bite and
lingers on the tongue.
The taste of danger.
[HIRO]
What are you...?
Sorry, would you have
preferred a kiss?
[HIRO]
A kiss?
[ZERO TWO] Oh, you guys
don't know about those, huh?
It's a special thing.
Y'know, I think I've
taken a liking to you.
How would you feel
about being my darling?
Your "darling"? Is that like
a partner or something?
Your ability's probably
still there, just lying dormant.
But I can awaken it for you.
Also, it's nice that you weren't
frightened by my horns at all.
[HIRO] When she held
out that hand, I...
[shuffling]
[ZERO TWO]
Too bad. Our time's up.
[CODE 081]
We've been looking for you.
Why do you keep running
off on your own?
It's not like we have
anything to do
till the welcome
ceremony tomorrow.
[CODE 081]
Well, as your partner,
I'm the one who suffers for it.
Her partner?
[CODE 081]
Are you a parasite cadet?
Your ceremony's tomorrow, right?
Sorry for any trouble she
may have caused you.
[HIRO]
It's fine.
When you say "partner,"
do you mean?
Let me give you some advice.
Stay far away from
this one, all right?
She's not the kind of pistil
that just anyone can handle.
Hold on! What's your name?
[ZERO TWO] My name? Do we
parasites even have names?
[HIRO grunts]
[ZERO TWO] Well, my code
is Zero-Zero-Two.
But everyone calls me
"Zero Two" for short.
[HIRO]
"So you're just like me."
That's what she said.
Getting mocked for my lack of
a partner would be one thing,
but the fact that there
was still some part of me
that wanted one...
...made me feel pathetic
and ashamed of myself.
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO]
I'm all too aware,
that a flightless bird
has nowhere to go.
Psst, look at all
those grown-ups.
[FUTOSHI] Yeah, they're all
here to see us. Crazy, huh?
[HIRO] "You're the
chosen ones," Papa said.
As far back as any of us
kids can remember,
we had code numbers
assigned to us,
and were told that piloting
weapons called FRANXX
in male-female pairs was
our one purpose in life.
We existed solely to fight.
[APE CHIEF]
Go out in a blaze of glory
and shed every last
drop of blood you have.
I pray that you become a shining
ray of hope for all humanity.
[CROWD cheers]
[HIRO] Children that aren't fit
for that purpose have no value.
Which is exactly why I
decided to leave this place.
[GORO]
Ichigo.
Focus on the ceremony.
Papa's watching.
[ICHIGO]
Right.
[HACHI] Those are the
official instructions
for your return
to the orphanage.
There anything else
you'd like to know?
[HIRO]
No, not really.
Code Zero-One-Six,
as you're aware,
HQ has offered you special
permission to remain here.
Are you sure you
don't wish to stay?
Yes, I am.
[HACHI]
Very well. I understand.
[HIRO gasps]
[NAOMI sobs]
[gasps]
[FEMALE PA VOICE] Positive
pulse and P-Factor dropping.
Timed out.
Commencing stage six linking.
Measuring ability score.
Negative pulse detected.
[gasps]
[FEMALE PA VOICE]
Positive pulse on standby.
Three, two, one. Timed out.
[pants]
[HACHI] Code Seven-Zero-Three
and Code Zero-One-Six.
You fail.
[NAOMI]
You should stay, Hiro.
So why aren't you? Did you
refuse because of me?
That's not it.
If I did stay here,
it's not like I would
be of use to anyone.
How incredibly typical
of you to think like that.
You're just running away.
From your partner and yourself.
You remember, right?
How many of our friends
disappeared from the orphanage?
There's no telling when we
could end up just like them.
So don't play the martyr!
Who cares if it's favoritism?
You're lucky you get
the chance at all!
[whimpers] We've made it so far!
I know I'd stay,
even if it killed me!
That's enough, knock it off.
Naomi.
[NAOMI] Why? Why did you
have to be my partner?
[FUTOSHI] So I gues Hiro
never showed, huh?
[ZOROME]
Ugh, forget that crybaby.
[MIKU]
Right up to the very end,
we could never tell what was
going through that kid's head.
I hope they get back
safe and sound.
Hiro and Naomi, that is.
But their ship probably
isn't going back
to the Garden, though.
I've never heard of a parasite
returning home before.
Are you all ready?
[PARASITES]
Yes, sir!
Well, take care, Hiro. I doubt
we'll see each other again.
My opportunity has passed us by.
But you still have a chance,
so make the most of it, okay?
You don't have to factor me
into your decisions anymore.
Hold on, Naomi!
[NAOMI, HIRO grunt]
But why?
[NAOMI] I don't need
those things anymore.
So please share
them with the others.
Wait, hold on!
You know something?
You probably don't realize,
but I really like this
name you gave me.
Hiro, I hope you
find a good partner.
Naomi.
[MALE OFFICER]
Hey, stop!
You can take the next
plant and still make it!
[HIRO]
Naomi.
I smell a klaxosaur.
[APE VICE CHIEF] We will now
commence the startup ritual.
With this, you children will at
last become official parasites.
What the...?
[FRANXX] This is bad.
The fog's rolling in.
What's the holdup? Get in there.
Um, I was thinking I'll--
[BOTH grunt]
What's that?
Those things weren't
there a second ago.
Naomi!
[MOHO KLAXOSAUR A roars]
[MOHO KLAXOSAUR A growls]
[MALE OFFICER A] A klaxosaur!
Prepare to intercept!
Klaxosaur... That thing?
[HIRO screams]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[MOHO KLAXOSAUR A roars]
[HIRO]
Wait, that's where. Damn it!
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO]
Another one?
[MALE OFFICER C] Klaxosaur!
Run for cover! Take shelter!
[FRANXX]
A moho-class, huh?
It's big and strong,
with a fine look.
This is no time to be
admiring its appearance!
We have to get out of here!
Hurry up and retrieve
the parasites!
What's going on out there?
[BOTH gasp]
[FEMALE PA VOICE A]
Garage Two damaged.
Unfit for housing Delphinium.
[gasps]
[MOHO KLAXOSAUR A roars]
Oh, great, now
there's a stampede?
[APE CHIEF] What a
wretched sight to behold.
Has she devoured another stamen?
[APE VICE CHIEF]
It's hard to tell which one
is the real monster here.
[MOHO KLAXOSAUR A roars]
[HIRO gasps]
You guys! What the--?
[MOHO KLAXOSAUR A roars]
[CROWD screams]
[HIRO grunts]
[HIRO screams]
[HIRO]
Ow. What was that?
[CODE 081 groans]
[HIRO gasps]
Hey. Are you all right?
[ZERO TWO]
Forget about him. He's a goner.
[HIRO] Wait, you're--
What are you doing in there?
What does it look like?
I'm going monster hunting,
of course.
You're gonna pilot this
thing all by yourself?
[ZERO TWO]
I gotta go.
Wait! Hold on a second!
You can't go like that!
[ZERO TWO]
Get off me!
[HIRO] This is crazy.
Besides, you're on your own now.
FRANXX can't be piloted alone.
[ZERO TWO] I'm always alone.
It's been like that forever.
I'm used to it.
Don't go! You'll die out there!
[ZERO TWO] So what?
I'm not afraid of death.
Sooner or later, that thing's
gonna start moving again.
And when it does,
everyone here is gonna die.
But I'm not afraid of death.
And even if I were,
I'd still have a job to do.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
[HIRO]
"I'm powerless. Right now,
I can't do anything to help my
friends, or fight a klaxosaur."
That's what I kept thinking.
But as I stared at the girl
standing in front of me,
for some reason,
the words that escaped
my lips were...
[HIRO] Wait. I'll pilot
that robot with you.
I'm not about to let you
do this on your own.
Oh? And are you prepared to die?
I don't know that.
But what I do know is, right
now, I don't belong anywhere.
Which means I might
as well be dead.
So please, take me with you!
[ZERO TWO] Mm. You really
are just like me.
You and I are very similar.
Haven't seen a human cry
in quite a long time.
I like the look in your eyes.
It makes my heart race.
[ZERO TWO]
Now, come to me.
Let me get a taste of you.
After all... you are
now my darling!
[HIRO gasps]
It's back up!
And heading this way!
Did it eat it?
[FRANXX]
No... That's...
When negative and positive,
the male and female factors,
combine, and their hearts
become one, the iron maiden
will reveal her true form.
[FRANXX]
Now this is a FRANXX!
Beautiful, isn't it?
You're the best, Strelizia!
Yeah, but who's piloting it?
[ZERO TWO]
Game over.
[ICHIGO]
So that's a FRANXX.
The kind of robot
we'll be piloting.
[HIRO] I don't know why,
but the warm touch of her lips
against mine made
my heart race.
Other than that, though,
I remember nothing of what
happened in that cockpit.
Hiro?
What's he doing in there?
[GORO] Wait, there's someone
with him. Are those...
[MIKU]
...horns?
[FUTOSHI]
You mean, that pistil is--?
[ICHIGO]
The Partner Killer.
Here, allow me to
introduce you all.
That's Zero-Zero-Two, she's with
the special forces unit.
Controlled by APE.
She's a girl that
carries klaxosaur blood.
[HIRO] However, after taking
this step of my own free will,
I felt like, finally, I might
be able to fly again.
I found you, my darling.