[HACHI] This mission
has but one objective.
Take control of the area
known as the Gran Crevasse.
The Fourth United Company
is carrying out attacks
as we speak. But, due to
klaxosaur resistance,
they're not making inroads.
You are to group with squads
from four other plantations
and take part in the mission
as the Sixth United Company.
Do we have an idea of what
exactly is in the Gran Crevasse?
[NANA grunts]
This might prove
shocking to you kids,
but you need to
know the situation.
[ZOROME] What is that?
Some kinda black wall?
[MIKU gasps] What the hell?
What's going on there?
[BOTH gasp]
[FUTOSHI]
No way.
[KOKORO]
How awful.
Compared to our prior battles,
this one's on a completely
different scale.
Taking over the Gran Crevasse
has been a long-standing
wish of Papa's.
This battle could be a turning
point in humanity's history.
[GORO gasps]
Hey, look.
[FRANXX]
Hmph. She devoured them all.
I should've known.
Silly hellcat.
[MALE SAGE A]
We're almost there.
If we can seize control
of the Gran Crevasse,
we may finally have our wish!
[MALE SAGE B] Hringhorni's
construction is proceeding
smoothly as well.
[MALE SAGE C]
If we have them both,
we can bury those pests
once and for all.
[FEMALE SAGE A]
The time has come!
[PAPA]
Where are you going, Werner?
[FRANXX]
I can't sit around here.
I want to watch it all happen
from a front-row seat.
Zero Two.
[CODE 090] Damn it! There are so
many of them, we can't link up!
[CODE 245 grunts]
What?
[CODE 498 screams]
[CODE 090]
Hold on! I'll be right--
[CODE 090 grunts]
[CODE 498 grunts, screams]
Let them go!
[grunts] What was
that? Strelizia?
[CODE 090 grunts]
What the...?
[9'a]
Hey. Good job hanging in there.
You did quite well for humans.
We'll take over now, so you
can go chill in the rear.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Message from Mission Command.
Sixth United Company,
prepare for sortie...
It's time! You're up, kids!
All right! We're gonna go kick
some klaxosaur butt! See ya!
Hey, don't take any of my
food while we're gone, okay?
[HIRO gasps]
[GORO] Come on, man,
there's no need to look so down.
You've got nothin'
to worry about.
We'll be fine, promise.
[HIRO]
Right.
All you need to do
is sit tight and wait.
Once this battle is over,
I'm going to teach you
how to pilot a FRANXX again
from the ground up.
[HIRO gasps]
You guys, please come
back alive.
[ALL chuckle]
[NANA] Your goal is Point F-Two.
All units, move out!
Bunch of scrubs! You're not
even good for a warm-up!
They may have the numbers.
but it doesn't matter!
Come on! How boring!
Entertain us more!
[9'a laughs]
Let's go!
[9'a chuckles]
One lot down. Next!
[MIKU] Wow. It's like we have
a bunch of Strelizias.
[ICHIGO]
C'mon, we're joining the fight.
[9'a] I wasn't expecting
there to be this many.
[9'g]
There's no end to them.
Alpha, see that? Your left.
[9'a whistles]
[9'b]
Who are they?
[9'g]
The children of Squad 13.
[9'e]
Alpha's shiny new toys.
[ICHIGO gasps]
[9'a]
Hey. So that's your FRANXX.
How truly adorable.
[ICHIGO]
Gee, thanks for the compliment.
Now, what's the situation?
[9'a] We're holding
them off just fine.
But we're not getting
any closer to our goal.
Look. You see that over there?
The Crevasse has been sealed
off within a thick dome.
To get rid of it, we'll have
to strike from the inside.
So, basically...
[ICHIGO]
We have to go through there.
Let's move, guys.
Argentea, Genista,
follow my lead.
Chlorophytum,
provide cover fire.
[ALL]
Roger!
[IKUNO]
We're going full power!
[FUTOSHI]
Right!
[IKUNO grunts]
[ICHIGO shouts]
[MIKU grunts, shouts]
[CODE 498]
What's going on over there?
[SQUAD 26 PILOT C]
I've never seen anyone fight
like that before.
It's Squad 13.
And they're as all over
the place as ever.
Glad they're here.
All right, let's take this
chance to regroup, everybody!
[SQUAD 26]
Yeah!
[KOKORO]
Mitsuru!
Right, here we go!
[GORO]
I see it!
Wait, it almost looks man-made.
[ICHIGO] We're going in through
that opening, everyone!
[GORO grunts]
[ZOROME]
What was that?
[IKUNO]
The klaxosaurs are fleeing.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Detecting magma energy
readings underground.
Reanalyzing signals...
[FRANXX] Oh? There was something
like that hidden down there?
Wait. A Super Lehmann-Class?
I've never even heard of that.
[gasps] The mountains
are moving!
That was our home.
Plantation 26.
[GORO] Oh, crap! It's going
around destroying plantations!
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Super Lehmann-Class klaxosaur
moving from point E3.
Three plantations lie
on its estimated course.
[APE VICE CHEIF] Get Code
Zero-Nine-Zero on the line.
We're moving to
Protocol Three-Two.
"Protocol Three-Two."
You're sure?
[APE VICE CHEIF]
Is something wrong?
Uh. No, sir.
[APE VICE CHEIF]
Code Zero-Nine-Zero,
you do realize this
is a great honor.
[CODE 090]
Yes. I understand.
[FEMALE OPERATOR A] The Super
Lehmann-Class klaxosaur
is heading right for us.
Estimated contact: 240 seconds.
It's going to hit us.
What do we do?
[MITSURU] No, it's moving
toward Plantation 13!
[ZOROME]
What? Seriously?
[9'a]
Well, what now?
Is that?
Oh, I see.
Go! Protocol Three-Two.
[SQUAD 26]
Roger.
[CODE 090]
This is for the best, right?
Squad 13, the rest
is in your hands.
[GORO grunts]
What the hell?
[ZOROME]
Hey! It stopped!
[GORO]
No.
[FUTOSHI gasps]
They're attacking our home!
[ICHIGO] And it's up to us
to defend it, so let's go!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[ICHIGO]
Zero Two?
[ZERO TWO growls]
[NANA]
Raise the bulwarks!
If we lose this place,
we're done!
[HACHI] Neutralizing the
Super Lehmann-Class
is our top priority...
Doctor! It isn't
safe for you here.
Please return to headquarters!
You get back
to Mistilteinn, Hiro!
[FRANXX] Don't you find her
more beautiful than any human?
Pure, and proud.
And more alone than us all.
Like a klaxosaur
through and through.
No! Zero Two isn't a klaxosaur!
[gasps]
[FRANXX] I thought she
had finally found a partner.
The poor girl.
Come on! How many
more do we have to kill?
[ZOROME] Quit whining, fatty!
We gotta protect our plantation!
[FUTOSHI]
Don't call me that!
[MIKU] Hey, why don't you
fire more of those beams
from earlier?
[IKUNO]
Because I don't have the energy!
And I've blown through
my reserves, too!
[MIKU]
What? No way!
[KOKORO] Don't start fighting.
We all have to work together!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[9'b] My, how scary.
She's in a foul mood today.
Imagine being on the bad
side of that unseemly beast.
It's enough to give me chills.
[ICHIGO]
Zero Two.
[HIRO] Zero Two. What were you
trying to tell me back then?
[HIRO gasps]
[HIRO] What am I...
What am I hesitating for?
[KOKORO]
We're being pushed back!
[MITSURU] We can't let
them get any farther!
[IKUNO shouts]
[IKUNO]
I'm out!
[FUTOSHI]
We may not have ammo...
...but we can still fight!
[MIKU grunts]
Hey!
[ZOROME]
Damn you!
We can't give in!
We have to defend the city!
[GORO]
Hey, Ichigo. Ichigo! Behind us!
[ICHIGO gasps]
We can't afford to lose focus.
[ICHIGO]
Sorry.
[GORO] Hold on. What's a
training unit doing here?
[ZOROME]
Whoa! What's the deal?
[MIKU] Wait. You guys!
Is that... Hiro?
[GORO]
That guy.
[HIRO]
When did it happen?
When was it that I
stopped asking questions?
[HIRO]
Back then, all I wanted
was to learn about
the outside world.
To set foot outside the Garden.
I was always fighting alone.
Nobody took a stand with me,
and that was frightening.
But, when I saw you...?
I realized there were others
fighting this world with me.
And that made me so, so happy!
[HIRO]
It has to be you.
Without you...
Without you, I can't fight!
I need you!
[ICHIGO]
Hiro! Why did you come out here?
What do you think you can
do in a training unit?
I'm not going to let you go!
[ICHIGO gasps]
[ICHIGO] Hey! Why are you
shutting us down, Goro?
Because I've seen enough.
[ICHIGO]
You what?
I can't stand it anymore.
Seeing them like this.
Hiro, get in.
[HIRO gasps]
You have something to
tell her, don't you?
[HIRO gasps]
All right. Make sure he
gets to Zero Two, Ichigo.
You're also worried
about her, aren't you?
[ICHIGO grunts]
[HIRO]
I'm sorry, Ichigo.
[ICHIGO] All of this boy-girl
stuff is really such a pain.
Let's go!
[ICHIGO]
Hiro's mind is entering mine.
[ZERO TWO]
...being my darling?
[ICHIGO]
What are these? Hiro's memories?
No... Don't show me these.
I'm finally connected
to Hiro, but this is...
[HIRO] Wait for me, Zero Two!
I'm coming to you!
Well, damn it.
It's all about her.
[ICHIGO whimpers]
[ICHIGO]
Here we go, Hiro!
[HIRO]
Yeah!
Good luck, bro.
[ZOROME, MIKU] Hey, what're you
acting all cool for?
[ZERO TWO growls]
[ZERO TWO]
How I longed to be human.
[ICHIGO]
Zero Two!
What are you doing?
Why're you--?
[ICHIGO grunts]
I've had enough.
I'm sick and tired of the
way you toy with me.
[ICHIGO shouts]
[HIRO]
Ichigo! Stop it!
[ICHIGO grunts] I wish...
that we'd never known you!
[ICHIGO grunts]
[ICHIGO] I'll let you
have Hiro, all right?
So, c'mon!
Get your act together!
[HIRO]
Zero Two, it's me.
I'm here. I came to see you.
[ICHIGO]
Keep them safe!
I hate to admit it,
but Strelizia's the only one
who can kill that giant lug!
[KOKORO grunts]
Their numbers are dwindling.
[MITSURU]
Even so, stay alert.
[MIKU] I've never killed
so many of them before.
[MIKU gasps]
[ZOROME] Hey, Miku.
There's something in there.
[MIKU]
What... is that?
[IKUNO]
It looks kinda human.
[MIKU] What? That's impossible.
Don't be stupid!
[FUTOSHI] Yeah, there's
no way it could b--
[MIKU gasps]
An explosion?
What the hell is this?
[FEMALE OPERATOR A]
Plantation 37's backup process
is currently 98% complete.
[PAPA]
They can go.
Let's release them from
the cages... of their bodies.
What's going on?
Yeah. Weren't adults
still inside there?
It's strange. Are they
making them self-destruct?
And there it goes.
[9'a]
It seems Papa and the rest
are planning to end
this without Strelizia.
[9'b] How many more
will be sacrificed?
[HACHI]
Who goes that far?
[FRANXX]
Of all the foolish...
Still not getting a response.
No choice left.
[HIRO]
Sorry, but I'm gonna touch you.
Please, just one more time.
Take me to where you are.
[MALE STAFF A]
Code Zero-One-Six's memory
alteration is complete.
As for Zero-Zero-Two, however,
there were some memories
we couldn't effect.
It felt like there was something
strong protecting them.
[MALE STAFF B] Erase those
memories, they're noise.
[MALE STAFF C]
Repeated use of the device
will put her under
too much strain.
[FRANXX]
It matters not.
[MALE STAFF B]
What do we do with Zero-One-Six?
[FRANXX]
Return him to the Garden.
He's probably useless now
that he's ingested her blood.
But he's an
interesting specimen.
[inaudible]
[ZERO TWO groans]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[ZERO TWO screams]
[ZERO TWO]
I didn't want to forget.
Because... I thought if I did,
then I would never be human.
[ZERO TWO]
The first word I learned was
how he referred to himself: "I."
After that came "Zero Two."
And then, the third was...
And that way I can
always be... your darling.
[ZERO TWO]
"Darling."
Darling! Darling! Darling!
[HIRO]
You never forgot, did you?
Y'know, I think I've
taken a liking to you.
How would you feel
about being my darling?
After all, you are
now my darling!
[HIRO]
Even as you were hurt so badly,
you kept fighting this
world all by yourself.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Darling?
[HIRO]
I finally got to see you!
No! Don't look!
Aren't you scared of me?
After all, you know I
used you this entire time.
That doesn't
matter anymore, okay?
But I... I called you fodder!
How can you ever forgive
me for saying that?
And I called you
a monster, remember?
So now we're even.
That's right. I am a monster!
That's why you--!
No it's not!
We've gotta talk it out!
You and I have to
think it through!
There must be places
we have to go!
Our journey begins now!
Surely this world
is much, much larger!
Larger than we can imagine!
We couldn't do it back then,
but this time, I know we can!
Let's see the outside
world together!
Zero Two. Together, we are one.
[ICHIGO]
How much longer, Hiro?
[FUTOSHI]
Oh, crap!
[IKUNO]
Strelizia!
[KOKORO]
Look!
[ICHIGO]
What's that light?
Doctor...
[FRANXX]
He did it!
[ALL]
Strelizia!
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO]
Darling!
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO] Darling! Darling!
Darling! Darling!
[ZERO TWO]
Darling! I'm so happy I met you!
I love you!
[HIRO whimpers, chuckles]
[HIRO]
Zero Two! I feel the same!
I love you, too!
Cut the comms
next time, dumbass.
Seriously.
[MIKU]
Yeah. Right? Stupid idiots!
[ICHIGO]
I'm happy for you. You both.
[HIRO] Zero Two, we need
to destroy that dome.
Think we can?
[ZERO TWO]
If we're together, of course!
[9'a] Well, then.
Shall we get going, too?
[HIRO yells]
[ZERO TWO, HIRO]
Go!
[9'a]
It's time. Let's do this!
[SPECIAL FORCES]
Yeah!
[KOKORO]
Oh, wow.
[APE VICE CHIEF]
The door to the Gran Crevasse
has been opened.
[PAPA] The day of humanity's
liberation is upon us.
[HIRO] The Jian, also known as
"the bird that shares wings"...
[ZERO TWO]
...only possesses one wing.
[HIRO]
Unless a male and female pair
lean on each other
and act as one...
[ZERO TWO]
...they're incapable of flight.
They're imperfect,
incomplete creatures.
[ZERO TWO, HIRO]
But...
[ZERO TWO]
...to me...
[HIRO]
[ZERO TWO, HIRO]
...their way of life...
...struck me as
profoundly beautiful.
[9'g]
Hey, look at that.
[9'e grunts] They won't let
it end so easily, huh?
[9'y] Is that a collective
mass of cores?
[9'b]
Damn, that's huge.
[9'a] We're out of time.
We better get out of here.
Before this entire area blows.
Zero Two. Let's go!
[ZERO TWO]
Hm!
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[9'a chuckles]
Wow, an instant reaction.
[GORO gasps]
We're still alive.
[IKUNO]
But what was that thing?
[ICHIGO]
A... massive hand?