[HIRO] Had I really
forgotten all this time?
How did I forget
something so important?
[HIRO]
That was you. You were the girl.
The one with the
picture book back then.
[ZERO TWO gasps]
You saw?
[HIRO]
I'm sorry. I...
[ZERO TWO gasps]
[HIRO] I didn't remember.
But our minds linked.
And this happened before, too.
Even then, you were
waiting under the tree...
...for me.
But how?
[gasps]
--[HIRO grunts]
--[ZERO TWO] Darling!
So... it's you?
You're my darling
from back then?
All this time...
what have I been doing?
[door hisses]
[ICHIGO]
Get your hands off him!
[GORO gasps]
Zero Two. You okay?
Answer me!
[ZERO TWO] "I want you to always
speak your mind with me."
[ZERO TWO] "I want to get
to know you better."
[ZERO TWO]
He often told me,
that he wanted us to
understand each other.
[ZERO TWO] At first, I couldn't
comprehend what he meant.
What he was trying to say.
But... I think I get it now.
I think... I know what
he was looking for.
♪
[NANA] It looks like he's
at the end of his rope.
His yellow blood cell count's
reached an alarming number.
It's beyond what the
human body can handle.
Saurification could begin
at any moment now.
Not to mention
his brain's condition.
His mind's trapped in a haze.
Did he connect
with Zero-Zero-Two
via Strelizia too deeply
and hallucinate?
Either way, he's in
a perilous state.
I thought Hiro might be able
to handle pairing with her,
but it's time to call this off.
--[ICHIGO] Hold it. Hey!
--[ZERO TWO] I'll talk...
--[ZERO TWO] ...to my darling.
--I'm talking to you!
[ZERO TWO]
That way...
[ICHIGO]
I told you to wait!
[grunts]
Don't try to stop me. I need
to see my darling immediately.
You can't be serious!
Do you realize who put
Hiro in that hospital bed?
You're not going
anywhere near him again!
[GORO]
Let's calm down, Ichigo.
I mean, she must be worried
about him too, you know.
[MIKU]
That's right. Come on.
Why are you getting
so worked up?
[ICHIGO] You've deceived
Hiro and exploited him
from the beginning!
And if that wasn't enough,
you tried to make him
lose his humanity!
[MITSURU, IKUNO sigh]
Wait up, "lose his humanity"?
[ICHIGO] It's true. I've heard
how you suck up your partner's
life and discard them
when you're done.
And Hiro's not the first,
you've killed many,
many people that way!
Who told you that?
I overheard Nana
and Hachi, too.
And if it keeps up, Hiro can
no longer be called human.
[MIKU]
Huh?
Everything she said. Is it true?
Of course, it isn't. No way.
Something's mixed up.
The two of you have gotten
on just fine so far--
You shut your mouths.
What I do to my darling
is none of your damn business,
you understand?
[ICHIGO]
Then you admit it?
If it makes you happy.
My darling's waiting.
[ICHIGO grunts] You know, at
first I had misgivings about
having you as part
of our team.
But... you started to fit in,
and I thought we'd finally
become teammates.
Us, teammates? I couldn't
care less about that.
[gasps]
[ZERO TWO]
Now outta my way.
[ICHIGO]
Well, I don't care how you feel.
Because... you'll never
see Hiro again.
[ZERO TWO growls]
[ICHIGO]
This entire time.
You've been deceiving him
and us! Not anymore.
You have no place here!
[KOKORO gasps]
[ICHIGO gasps]
Hiro!
[KOKORO]
Thank goodness!
[GORO]
Hey.
Welcome back.
[ZOROME]
Man!
I thought you were a goner for
sure this time, but nope!
Good job surviving again!
They said if you get some rest,
you'll be as good as new in
no time. Isn't that great?
[HIRO]
Yeah...
Anyway... Where's Zero Two?
[ICHIGO] She isn't here.
I didn't let her come.
You know why, don't you?
[ICHIGO]
There's no need to worry.
[HIRO grunts]
[ICHIGO]
We're gonna keep you safe.
But for now, you should
get some rest.
Ichigo.
[GORO]
See ya, Hiro.
--[KOKORO] Take care.
--Oh, sure.
[FUTOSHI]
Don't forget to eat, okay?
[HIRO]
Mitsuru.
What did you wanna
talk to me about?
Way back... before you
got an Elixir Injection,
I made a promise to you.
I guess, after that, I...
[MITSURU] Never mind.
It was a long time ago.
Even I'd forgotten
about it until now.
Really?
[MITSURU]
Yeah.
You know any other stamen
would've died long ago.
I see you've still got the
devil's luck on your side.
Listen to Ichigo.
Learn your lesson and
stay away from Zero Two.
The thing is, there's something
that I have to ask her,
so I can't.
[MITSURU]
There you go.
Poking your nose
into trouble again.
That part of you
hasn't changed a bit.
[HIRO]
Mitsuru. Thanks.
"Ask her," huh?
After that day, my aptitude
scores kept going down...
...until finally...
[HACHI] Code Seven-Zero-Three
and Code Zero-One-Six.
You fail.
[HIRO]
My life ended once already.
But, through meeting Zero Two...
I did it.
[laughs] I'm doing it!
I'm piloting!
[HIRO] Still, if no other
stamen could handle it...
...why could I?
[ZERO TWO] You'll be fine.
Next and every other time.
[HIRO] There's only one
reason I can think of.
[HIRO grunts]
[ZERO TWO] Now. Let me
get a taste of you.
After all, you are
now my darling!
[HIRO]
Did you know...
...that I could only
ride with you all along?
[HIRO grunts]
[HIRO] That's it. I have to
ask her. I need to be sure.
[HACHI]
You have your next mission.
HQ sent the official orders.
Plantation 13 has been heading
towards a certain place
for a while.
This is our destination.
Your mission, is to neutralize
every klaxosaur inhabiting
this structure, and take
control of this area.
[NANA] Furthermore, this will be
a joint operation with the Nines
and FRANXX squads
from each plantation.
Wait, we're teaming up?
[HACHI] In 27 hours from now,
the opening salvo will be fired.
[ZOROME grunts]
[HACHI]
And you'd best be ready.
Squad 13 is scheduled to
be part of the sixth wave.
Get it over with already.
[NANA] Unlike past missions, the
enemy will counter with numbers.
This will, without a doubt,
be your most difficult operation
to date. Focus on the--
Ichigo?
Before the mission
gets underway,
please remove Code
Zero-Zero-Two from Squad 13.
[gasps]
[NANA grunts]
Actually, the thing is--
If this request isn't granted,
we'll have no choice.
Squad 13 will not participate
in the operation.
You must understand, this was
our decision as a whole.
The simple fact is, we can't
fight with her anymore.
As it happens, Zero Two was
set to return to the Nines
as of this mission, anyway.
[ICHIGO gasps]
Just wait a second!
Where'd that come from?
Don't go making
decisions for me!
[NANA] HQ has already given
the green light. It's final.
We can't keep you
here any longer.
[ZERO TWO]
What about my darling?
[NANA sighs]
[ZERO TWO gasps]
Uh, where are you heading?
[ZOROME] Sorry, Zero Two, but
you're not going to his room.
We won't let you
see him, period.
[ZERO TWO grunts]
[ZERO TWO]
Why?
[HIRO]
Hm?
Sorry, Hiro.
[HIRO]
Hm?
But you really should
get back to your bed.
[HIRO]
Uh, but...
[MIKU]
Please.
[HIRO sighs]
[ZERO TWO] Why? Why is
everyone getting in my way?
All I want... is to
see my darling...
...and talk to him.
[knocking]
You're up. Feeling all right?
Yeah. A lot better than before.
That's good. I'm glad.
How're things?
Well...
Here, I brought you
an apple. Want some?
[ICHIGO] Anyway. Zero Two's
going back to the Nines.
What? How soon?
[ICHIGO] Tomorrow night.
We have a big mission coming up.
[HIRO exhales]
[ICHIGO]
You hate me. Don't you?
[HIRO]
Huh?
I know you want to see her,
but regardless, you can't.
I can't let you. If you do,
you'll never be the same again.
[HIRO sighs]
[ICHIGO] The others are
worried too. We're a team now.
We don't wanna lose anyone.
[ICHIGO] So please, Hiro,
I don't care if you hate me,
but please don't go anywhere.
[HIRO gasps]
Sorry, Ichigo.
Maybe I can't help it.
Mitsuru told me I
have a tendency
to poke my nose into trouble.
[ICHIGO]
Huh?
I guess... I really did make
all of you worry, didn't I?
[gasps]
[ICHIGO] Yeah, but you
don't have to apologize.
That's the good thing about you.
Honestly, I've always found
that side of you to be--
[ICHIGO grunts]
[HIRO gasps]
Ow.
[HIRO]
You okay?
Yeah, it's nothing.
Oh, man, that's a
pretty deep cut.
[HIRO]
There. You're all set.
Kind of hard to tell which
of us is supposed to be
the patient here, huh?
[HIRO]
Seriously.
You always were a bit on
the clumsy side, Ichigo.
I just have bad
luck occasionally!
That so? Then what about this?
Well, uh, clearly, it's a bunny.
It is? You're kidding.
Hey! Don't pick on me!
I'm gradually getting
better at it!
This one here is actually
close to the real thing! See?
Those kinda sorta almost
look like its ears.
[ICHIGO] And I thought,
we'd finally become teammates.
Not anymore.
You have no place here!
[ZERO TWO growls]
[ZERO TWO]
I always knew.
No matter how I disguised
myself as a human,
I could never be one of you.
That's why I wanted to
kill lots more klaxosaurs.
And quickly. To become human.
[ZERO TWO]
For that, I...
But even then, all I
have... is my darling.
--[crashing]
--[BOTH gasp]
[HIRO]
Thanks, Ichigo.
[HIRO sighs]
Think I'll get some sleep now.
[ICHIGO] Oh. Right.
Sorry if I stayed too long.
[HIRO]
Oh!
I'll have them clean
up the mess later.
You can leave it there.
Sure. But don't forget, okay?
[ICHIGO]
See ya, Hiro. Take care.
[HIRO grunts]
[ZOROME]
Wh--? Hey!
[FUTOSHI]
Hold it right there!
[ICHIGO chuckles]
[crashing]
[ZOROME]
Stop already!
[FUTOSHI] Did you hear us?!
Get back to your room!
[GORO]
Zero Two, what're you--?!
--[GORO grunts]
--[KOKORO gasps]
Goro, are you okay?
[GORO groans]
[ICHIGO gasps]
Hey. What's going on here?
Well, she, uh...
She got loose.
Don't you stop me.
I am going to see my darling.
That's enough!
Just give it a rest!
You'll see him and then what?
You lie to him again?
[ZERO TWO grunts]
You're wrong. You're wrong,
you're wrong!
I just... want to
talk to my darling!
[GORO]
Let her see him, Ichigo.
We should listen to her.
She must have something
important to say.
Goro. You know what she's done.
[KOKORO]
I agree with him.
We can't keep forcing
them apart like this.
I feel so sorry for them.
[ICHIGO grunts]
You can see Hiro.
On the one condition that
we're all present when you do.
Are you okay with that?
[ZERO TWO grunts]
--[footsteps]
--[MIKU gasps]
What the...?
What's going on here?
How's Hiro?
Probably sleeping.
He's been really quiet.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro? We're coming in.
Darling, I--
[ICHIGO gasps]
Huh? What?
[MIKU] No way! I kept
watch the entire time!
Do you see that?
[MIKU, FUTOSHI gasp]
[GORO]
That guy.
[IKUNO]
He got out from there?
Reckless as always.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro... Why?
[ZERO TWO]
You tricked me.
You... lied to me.
No! We didn't plan for this
to happen. Believe us!
He must've-- That's it!
He left to find you!
[ZERO TWO]
Shut up!
Zero Two, it's me.
I um... I have a question.
And there's something
I wanna talk about.
Do you remember when you said
you weren't afraid to die?
I'm the same.
But that's why I wanna make
sure of, well, several things.
Like, did you...?
[HIRO] Did you use me?
Knowing all along?
[HIRO]
Zero Two? Are you--
[gasps]
[HIRO]
What happened?
[HIRO gasps]
--[ZERO TWO giggles]
--[ALL groan]
[ZERO TWO]
You humans are so weak.
Now do you get it? I won't
let anyone stand in my way.
[HIRO]
Zero Two!
[ZERO TWO]
Darling.
What're you doing?
I had to see you, darling.
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
Ichigo! Are you okay?
Talk to me. Ichigo.
[ICHIGO]
Hiro... Run away.
[HIRO gasps]
Why would you do this?
[ZERO TWO]
"Why"?
You asked me to speak
my mind with you, remember?
When I tried, these guys
wouldn't let me, so I...
[HIRO]
No.
[ZERO TWO]
Let's talk. Lots and lots, okay?
It's not too late.
We can still take it back--
Zero Two! Right now,
you truly are a monster.
You aren't human.
[ZERO TWO]
This... is punishment.
I set up the boy who
was the sole reason
I wanted to be human.
I tried to make him the
same kind of monster as me.
And this is my punishment.
[FUTOSHI groans]
[door clatters]
I'm sorry, but this
was for the best, Hiro.
Let's go in--
[gasps]
[HIRO, ICHIGO gasp]
[ICHIGO]
You can't! I won't let you!
I'm not letting you go!
Because if you go
back to Zero Two,
you'll turn into a monster!
You won't be the
same ever again!
I'd rather die than
let that happen!
[HIRO sighs]
But I...
[HIRO gasps]
Welcome home.
Nine Iota. Take a look.
The doctor brought a good
selection here all for you.
Use as many as you like.
[HIRO gasps]
[GORO gasps]
[ICHIGO] Our kiss, the one we
shared in the mock battle.
I don't regret it. I want
to be with you. Forever.
I'll make it so I can ride
with you this time, I swear.
I can do anything if
I'm doing it for you, Hiro.
It's true... I mean...
I've... The thing is...
You've always been
my everything!
I've known. Ever since
we were little kids!
I've always had eyes
for you and you alone.
I love...
I love you, Hiro!
[engine roars]