[COMMENTATOR]
The scores are pretty far apart,
but if Kumabara
can hold 'em,
they've got a chance.
The bleachers behind third
are going nuts out there!
Suzuki on the mound...
[KYON]
Something's... wrong.
That's what it felt like anyway.
I didn't care about the
baseball game on TV
'cause it was between
some other schools.
For some reason,
I got into anyway,
and started rooting
for the losing team.
[KYON] And that's when I got the
feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
[phone rings]
What does she want?
Your phone's ringing, Kyon.
I know; you don't
have to tell me.
[HARUHI]
Hey, you're free, right? Good.
Meet us at 2:00 in front of
the station. And don't be late!
[dial tone]
[KYON] I didn't have a
chance to say anything.
[phone rings]
[KYON]
Now, what?
[HARUHI]
I forgot to tell you,
make sure to bring your swim
trunks and some money, too.
Oh, wait, and your bike.
Definitely bring your bike.
That's it. Over and out!
[dial tone]
[KYON]
Well, that was weird.
It was like I knew what
Haruhi was gonna say
--before she even said anything.
--[metal clink]
[COMMENTATOR]
What a shot!
It's a big, fat hit...
[KYON]
Yeah... No...
Actually, it felt
like we'd had that
exact same conversation before,
like déjà vu or something.
[COMMENTATOR] Chalk up
another run for Jyonan.
That makes eight runs this game.
[KYON]
Summer's almost over...
You're late again, Kyon!
Where's your motivation, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
You're the only reason
I showed up anyway.
[MIKURU giggles]
Thanks, that's really sweet.
Now that we're all present and
accounted for, we can get going!
Where to?
[HARUHI] To the public swimming
pool. Where do ya think?
[KYON] That figures...
considering the stuff I brought.
We've got lots of summer
vacation-y things to do
during our summer break!
But we've only so
much time because
once it's gone,
it's gone for good!
We have to do what
we can, while we can
during our one and only
summer as tenth graders!
It's up to Kyon and Koizumi
to get us to the pool.
I know I'm gonna
hate asking this,
but what did you
mean by that last thing?
You guys are taking
us there on your bikes!
[sighs]
[HARUHI inhales]
Mm, can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes
it feel like summer!
[laughs]
Woo-hoo!
[KYON]
Restrain thyself!
Canst thou not see
the "no diving" signs?
[gasps]
Hurry up and get in, guys!
The water's warm! It's perfect!
[MIKURU]
Huh?
--[MIKURU whimpers]
--[HARUHI laughs]
[BOTH scream]
Doesn't that look like fun?
I mean, seeing Miss
Suzumiya enjoy the day
in such a normal fashion.
It's rather charming,
don't you think?
First, she called me up
and told me what to bring,
And then,
she demanded I meet her
without telling me
what was going on.
I'm sorry, but I don't
see anything charming
or normal about that.
[KOIZUMI]
Well, when she gets an idea,
she tends to strike
while the iron's hot.
[KYON] Yeah, but every time she
strikes, something goes wrong.
And by wrong, I might
nightmarishly wrong.
You have a point,
but it's peaceful
enough around here.
And as long as Miss Suzumiya's
laughing and having a good time,
we don't have to worry about
any earth-shattering events.
[gasps]
Now what is it?
It's nothing...
Just my imagination, I guess.
With everything that's
happened since we met,
you could say I've
become slightly paranoid.
[KYON]
Hpmh.
[gasps]
Let's race one more time!
--It's like--
--[MIKURU yelps]
[MIKURU]
Huh?
[KYON]
Yum! It's strawberry-licious!
[HARUHI laughss]
[GROUP laughing]
[HARUHI]
Get it!
[KYON]
Geez...
Now I know why they call it
a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone
in town's here today.
I wonder why Haruhi
chose this place.
[KYON]
Hm?
[KYON] There's that
weird feeling again.
It's like I've seen
this happen before.
Nagato, sitting there...
all alone, looking bored.
--[HARUHI] Kyon!
--[KYON gasps]
[KYON] Yeah... And then
Haruhi shows up and says...
[KYON, HARUHI] "So, these two
guys are my brigade members.
They do what I say,
so if you want
something, ask them!"
[CHILDREN]
Okay!
[HARUHI]
Time for some fun!
Let's go play water soccer!
Yeah, sure...
[KYON] Oh, well.
Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
[HARUHI] I've been thinking
of some fun things to do,
so I came up with this.
What is that thing for?
[HARUHI] It's a schedule
of how we're gonna
spend the rest of
our summer vacation!
[KYON]
A schedule for who?
For us, that's who!
We've only got two
weeks of vacation left.
That fact alone blew me away.
We've done a lot of cool things,
but we're running outta time.
There's still a bajillion
more things left for us to do.
I say, we gotta
pick up the pace!
[KYON]
Two weeks to do all that?!
[HARUHI] Mikuru, is there
anything else you wanna do?
[MIKURU]
Um...
I think I'd like to
try goldfish scooping.
[HARUHI]
Okay!
Goldfish scooping, it is.
[KOIZUMI]
Could I see that?
Okay, thanks.
We'll start the list tomorrow!
Do you guys know if there's a
bon festival happening anywhere?
Or a place to see fireworks?
[KYON] Why don't you
find that stuff yourself?
I can check around for those.
I'll call you if
I find anything.
[HARUHI]
Perfect!
I'll leave it up to you!
[HARUHI]
That's it for today! See ya!
Hey, Nagato?
Uh, well... It's nothing
important or anything,
but I was just wondering...
Is everything okay?
[NAGATO]
It is.
That's good to hear.
[NAGATO]
Yes.
Okay...
[KYON]
That's it. You can go.
Sorry to keep you.
[KYON]
What was that?
Why'd I want to talk to her?
[KYON] And just like that,
Koizumi managed to find
a bon festival happening
the very next day.
Wow!
So this is what festivals
were like back in this time.
[KYON] I guess I shouldn't
be surprised it's so crowded.
[HARUHI]
Look, Mikuru!
They've got goldfish
scooping over there,
just like you wanted!
Let's catch a ton and
break some scoopers!
[KYON]
Don't break the scoopers.
I didn't know you were
into stuff like that.
I got it.
No.
[NAGATO]
That one.
Okay, it's yours for 800 yen!
[VENDOR]
Thanks!
[KYON] I wish she would've
let me buy that for her...
It's the least I could do
after all she's done for us.
[HARUHI]
What an unbelievable haul!
But, I don't have room
for all those fish,
so I just kept two for us!
Anyway, let's go shoot
off some fireworks!
It's the perfect way
to end the day!
[KYON] Come on!
Don't you ever get tired?
Oh, well. If anything,
Haruhi's endless energy
is one her better qualities.
[HARUHI laughing]
[KYON yells]
[KYON]
Reckless as always.
It was summer,
and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I
wanted to forget about it.
Truth was, I couldn't
ignore it any longer.
Tomorrow, we're gonna
catch some bugs.
[KYON]
I don't want to spoil your fun,
but have you finished
your homework yet?
You gotta be kidding.
That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it
in like three days.
Three days?!
[HARUHI] You have to
get rid of that junk first,
so you can spend the
rest of your summer
having fun and not
worrying about it!
That's the only way to get
the most out of your vacation!
[KYON] Why does she
have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs
weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying
up the stats for us.
So anyway, tomorrow we're
gonna go bug-catching!
And the prize for catching
the most bugs is gonna be...
Um... He, he, the winner gets
to be brigade leader for a day!
[KYON] That's the last
thing I'd wanna be!
That sounds like a lot of fun,
but can we catch just
any random bug?
No... Only cicadas!
That's it, I'm calling it
the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest!
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] The next day was another
beautiful day, sunny and bright.
And the winner of the
contest ended up being...
You guessed it, Haruhi.
It's important to
follow the spirit of
catch and release
with these guys.
I mean, if we let
'em go this time,
they might come back
and return the favor!
[KYON] If something
were to come back and
return the favor of being
randomly captured and released,
I'd say they'd have to
be as dumb as a bug.
Hurry! Go back to the mountains!
[cicadas chirping]
[KYON gasps]
[MIKURU]
Wel-Welcome to our store!
[KYON] The next day,
our fearless leader
got us some part-time jobs.
[KOIZUMI]
Would you like a balloon?
No?
[NAGATO]
Take it.
Gimme!
[KYON]
Sure...
Thank you!
[KYON] Wearing a costume
in heat like this isn't a job.
It's more like a
test of endurance.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Like I said, our pay is the
costume Mikuru's wearing.
I've had my eye on this little
guy for a long time now.
The manager gave it to us 'cause
Mikuru looks so cute in it!
[KYON]
We worked in the sun,
sweat pouring down
our foreheads...
...for that?!
We'll keep this froggy in the
club room as a souvenir.
And Mikuru, you can wear him
whenever you want to, okay?
You have my permission!
[KYON gasps, grunts]
[sighs]
[phone rings]
[KYON grumbling]
[KYON]
Dammit...
Hello?
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON yells]
[MIKURU]
Kyon...
Miss Asahina, is that you?
[MIKURU sobbing]
Yes... It's me...
Something... really bad...
...don't know...
Is this really Miss Asahina?
[KOIZUMI]
Oh, hello! It's Koizumi.
How about you tell me
what you're doing
with her at this hour?!
[KOIZUMI]
We have a bit of situation here.
And it's a pretty
dire one, at that.
You could even say
it's an emergency.
[tires screeching]
Sorry we had to
call you out so late.
[KYON]
Miss Asahina! What happened?
I'm gonna kill you, Koizumi!
Oh, Kyon...
[sniffle]
I-I can't go back to the future!
[sobs]
[MIKURU sobbing]
Because I have to
classified information,
I used classified information
to get in touch with the future.
I haven't gotten any classified
information for about a week.
And I started to think how
weird that was, and I...
I was so surprised, I classified
information, I really did.
But it was classified
information, too.
And now I don't know what to do!
[KYON] Are all the classified
information things
you're talking about,
stuff you can't say on TV?
[KOIZUMI]
I'll explain it the best I can.
We're stuck in a time loop
that seems to infinite.
[KYON]
Huh?!
[KOIZUMI] We're repeating
every day between
August the 17th
through the 31st.
You see, time doesn't exist
after September the 1st.
It's only natural Miss Asahina
can't go back to the future,
when there's no future to go to.
There's nothing natural
about not having a future.
I mean, who's gonna
believe such a thing?
Actually, we were sort of
hoping you would believe it.
[KYON] They say,
"Believe and you'll be saved,"
but I've yet to be saved
from anything, even once.
Well, what's causing this
to happen? Got any ideas?
Wait, you mean you
don't already know?
I don't want to, so there.
[KOIZUMI]
It's Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON chokes, sighs]
I'm sure she doesn't even
realize it's happening.
It's a result of her
subconscious desires.
She wants summer
vacation to last forever.
[KYON]
You're kidding!
She still hasn't had enough fun?
[KOIZUMI]
That's what I think.
Perhaps she feels there's
something else that needs
to happen before our summer
vacation can really be over.
[KYON] Oh, man...
The trouble she gets us into
is always galactic in scale.
Well, anyway, at least now
I have an explanation
for all those weird feelings
of déjà vu I've been having.
You too? Do you
think it's possible
other people are having
the same feelings?
I doubt it, but you
and I are different.
The only people who can sense
this strange thing happening
are the ones who are
closest to Miss Suzumiya.
However, there's someone
who doesn't seem
to be affected by these
feelings of déjà vu.
As a matter of fact,
this person remembers
everything that's happened.
Well, are you gonna tell
me who it is or what?
I think you already
know that, too.
Is that true?
It is.
You can remember everything?
I can.
Then, how many times has
this happened to us?
This would be
15,532 times so far.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred thirty-two?
Nagato, I'm having a hard
time processing all this.
[gulps] But are you serious?
I am.
[KYON] You're saying we've
done the exact same things,
every time, that many times?
[NAGATO]
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,532 repetitions,
we did not attend a bon festival
the 2,391st time and
the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival
but did not go to
a goldfish scooping
booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time
jobs 9,056 times
and performed six
different types of jobs.
In addition to handing
out balloons, we worked as
--movers, cashiers--
--[KYON] Stop!
Okay... I got it.
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred thirty-two times...
That's what Nagato said.
Times two weeks...
That's, uh... 595 years!
She's the only one who
remembers everything we've done.
And she's had to repeat
those same things,
over and over again.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the
same things that many times?
[sighs]
[KYON] That's gotta be
the craziest story ever.
[KYON] The next night,
we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony
of Nagato's apartment.
And at first, Haruhi was
all over that telescope.
But eventually...
Oh, man. I wish I knew
what else she wants to do.
That's the question, isn't it?
If we knew the answer,
we'd be well on our way
to solving this thing.
I have an idea we
can try if you want.
What if someone were to grab
Miss Suzumiya from behind,
and then whispered, "I love
you," right into her ear?
[KYON]
And who's gonna be doing this?!
Can you think of anyone
better suited for that role?
[KYON]
My turn! I summon my veto card!
[KOIZUMI]
All right. How about if I do it?
[chuckles]
I'm just kidding.
I don't think I could pull
that role off anyway.
Besides, it would just
confuse Miss Suzumiya.
[KOIZUMI laughs]
[KYON]
Hmph.
We chugged along,
doing all kinds of
summer vacation things.
We went to a real
fireworks show,
and we even signed up for
a goby fishing tournament.
We did the test of courage,
watched some movies,
went to the beach,
bowling, even karaoke.
We were always doing something,
always on the move.
And the whole time,
all I could think was that
none of it was going to
be enough for Haruhi.
But, I couldn't do
anything about it.
So, I just bit my
lip and watched
as the last days of our
summer vacation went by.
And then, before I knew it,
August the 30th was here.
[HARUHI]
Hmm.
Well, that's it. We finished
everything on our list.
I know we did a lot, but now
I wonder if we did enough.
Hmm... Oh, well. Yeah,
I guess we did do a lot.
Unless there's something
else you guys wanna do?
[MIKURU whimpers]
[HARUHI]
Hmm.
Oh, okay then.
We pretty much did everything
we set out to do this summer,
so I guess that's enough.
[KYON]
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
[gasps]
I guess that's it for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can
take the day off now.
I'll see you guys at the
club room on Monday!
[KYON]
Wait, Haruhi!
[Kyon gasps]
[KYON]
There's that feeling again!
And it's stronger
than all the others!
Now I know we've done this
ten thousand times before,
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up re-living the past
two weeks again and again!
But, what should I do?
There must've been a clue
in something Haruhi said.
But what? What? What?!
Come on! Remember!
It's something
I'm worried about,
but I'm putting it
off for some reason.
If I don't do something now,
she'll go home!
I can't let that happen!
If I do, nothing will change!
Try to remember!
What've we done up till now?
What didn't we do?!
[growls]
There's no time to
think about it anymore.
It doesn't matter
if it doesn't work.
Just say something, anything!
[gasps]
Hang on a second!
We're not done yet!
[HARUHI]
Huh?!
Homework! Homework!
What are you talking about?
None of my homework's done!
I haven't even started it yet!
My summer can't be over
until I finish it!
Are you nuts?
Koizumi! Did you
finish your homework?
No, uh, we were so busy,
I'm only half-way done with it.
Let's do it together!
You too, Nagato.
I bet you're not done yet.
And you're coming with us,
Miss Asahina.
Uh, where are we going?
We're all gonna
meet at my house!
Bring all your notebooks
and textbooks,
and we'll work on it together!
We'll finish our summer
activities once and for all!
Nagato, Koizumi, I need to
copy whatever you've got.
Roger that!
We're gonna start first
thing tomorrow morning.
And we're gonna go
all day until we finish!
[HARUHI]
Hold it right there!
[growls]
How dare you give the orders?!
I'm the brigade leader,
and as your superior,
you need to get my
permission first!
Who do you think you are, huh?!
Acting without my permission
is against the rules!
[KYON gasps]
[HARUHI growls]
I wanna come over, too!
[alarm beeps]
[KYON]
It looks like I hit the jackpot.
[KOIZUMI] Miss Suzumiya is
a smart and talented person.
She's always been that way,
and she always will be.
And that's probably why
it never occured to her
that summer homework
could also be a bit of a
pain for others.
[KOIZUMI]
Since she's never had to do
the study group thing before,
I can see how she'd overlook
an opportunity like that.
[KYON] It was the first
day of the new term.
I should have gone home by now,
but I ended up
coming here instead.
Koizumi showed up, too.
Probably for the same reason.
It was weird though.
Nagato wasn't there.
I couldn't tell
by looking at her,
but I'll bet she must've
been pretty exhausted.
[KYON] The thought of us
re-living the past two weeks
tens of thousands of times
seems like a bad dream.
I'm not at all surprised
you feel that way.
We don't share any memories
with the versions of us
who had to go through
15,531 time loops.
That's because on
the 15,532nd time,
we snapped back into
the normal time flow.
How about a game of poker?
[KYON]
Hm?
Yeah, sure. Why not? I don't
have any money though.
[KOIZUMI]
Then we'll play for fun.
[KYON]
I did get a lot of hints,
hints like those
feelings of déjà vu,
especially the last one.
I wonder if it could've
been a memory
sent by one of the
previous versions of us.
I'm here because of all the
us's, if that's even a word,
who had to repeat
those last two weeks.
That's the way I
have to think about it,
so that it wasn't
all for nothing.
If I did forget,
then I'd be like Haruhi,
who's unaware those
summers even happened.
[KYON]
Hm?
How many?
[KYON]
I'm good.
Then, so am I.
[KYON] If I had the chance
to live today all over again...
Whoa!
[KYON] I hope I remember to put
some cash down on this hand.