[KYON] During final exams,
Haruhi, who suffered a bout
of melancholy during
the Star Festival,
had recovered from the
aforementioned melancholy
enough to go back to doing
whatever she wanted to do.
However, as an adverse reaction
to her emotional improvement,
the blue-colored baton
of depression had been
handed off to me.
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] Haruhi always
seemed to have time
left over during an exam,
and today was no exception
About 30 minutes before pencils
down, she was sound asleep
in the desk behind me.
Annoying. Oh, it's annoying.
It's so annoying.
[KYON]
According to Haruhi,
there is no such
thing as a break
for the SOS Brigade.
Even during exam time, when all
the other clubs went on hiatus,
this mysterious brigade,
which wasn't really even a club,
was open every day
without a holiday.
Kinda like a convenient store...
[HARUHI]
Hey, come take a look at this.
[KYON]
What is it?
You can't tell what it is?
I've no idea.
I don't get it at all.
It's the logo for
the SOS Brigade.
A logo? That's funny, 'cause
to me, it looks more like
a drunken tapeworm
wrapped around a tube.
Well, take a closer look at it!
See, it says "SOS Brigade"
right there in the middle!
[KYON] Now that she pointed it
out, I can't really say for sure
whether I can or can't
see it, but I wouldn't
disagree with anybody if
they said it was or wasn't.
And how many negatives did
I just use in that sentence?
If somebody's got time,
total it up for me.
You're the one that's
got the most free time.
Anyway, I was thinking
of putting this thing
on the homepage of the
SOS Brigade website.
[KYON]
You mean, this pathetic website
that only has a homepage?
This website that you made isn't
getting us any visitors at all.
It's so frustrating.
There's nothing on here
that spices it up.
It's all because
you got in my way.
We'd've had a ton of hits
if you'd let me post
these erotic pics of Mikuru.
So I got to thinkin',
I should paste a cool logo or
symbol for the SOS Brigade
on the homepage.
[KYON] Just get this stupid
excuse for a website
off the net already.
The access counter hasn't
even reached three digits yet,
and 90% of those hits have been
you checking the site for hits.
Write a blog on
there or something.
Isn't it your job
to keep a record
of the brigade's activities?
Ugh, too much of a hassle.
[KYON]
Well, it's a hassle for me, too.
Okay, Kyon, your job for
today is to make this logo
show up on the homepage
of the website.
[KYON]
Why don't you do it yourself?
I'm the brigade leader! It's
the job of the brigade leader
to give the orders!
Besides, if I did everything,
there'd be nothing left for you
guys to do, isn't that right?
I'm always spelling this stuff
out for you, why don't you
use your head? How do you
expect to improve yourself
if you only do what you're told?
There you go, talking
in circles again.
Are you telling me to do it
or not to do it? Which is it?
[HARUHI]
Enough! Get on it!
[sighs]
[KYON] Reluctantly, I shrunk the
master painter Haruhi's tapeworm
into an appropriate size. Then,
I pasted it, still reluctantly,
into the file, and uploaded it.
Starting tomorrow and lasting
until summer vacation,
we get to have our exam break.
It's also the time when my
teacher's mark my answers wrong.
Damn, that's annoying.
Guess I'll go and ogle
Miss Asahina for some comfort.
I knocked on the door, fully
expecting Miss Asahina's voice
to call out a wispy
"Yes" in reply.
--[knocks]
--[HARUHI] Come in.
[KYON]
You're the only one here?
Yuki's here, too.
[KYON] She's more like
an accessory to the room,
so you can't really
count her as a member.
I mean, officially, she's a
member of the Literary Club,
so I guess I should
correct myself.
You and Nagato are
the only ones here?
[HARUHI] You wanna file
a complaint about it?
[KYON] If I wrote down every
complaint I had about you,
it would fill up an entire sheet
of A4-size paper, both sides.
When you knocked on
the door just now,
I thought for sure we were
going to have a visitor today.
[KYON] Just being careful. I
don't wanna accidentally walk in
while Miss Asahina's changing.
[KYON] That lovely, innocent
young girl just can't seem
to figure out how
to lock a door.
So now, what's all
this about a visitor?
Don't tell me you
don't remember?
[KYON] I hope she isn't
gonna say anything
about the Star Festival
three years ago.
Oh, come on, it's
something you did,
and without getting
my permission first.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Those posters you put up
all over the school.
Right, those things.
[KYON]
Those posters were my attempt
at getting the student council
to keep the SOS Brigade alive
as a sort of jack-of-all-
-trades counseling thing.
I even drew them all
and stuck them up
on every bulletin board
in the school.
[HARUHI]
Anyway, take a look at this.
Something weird's
happening here.
Maybe it's just the
computer acting up.
[KYON] The SOS Brigade's logo
was warped, as if somebody used
a gathering filter on it.
On top of that, the counter
and title were gone.
It was subtle, but it was
different from the page I made.
It looks like the file on
the server has been corrupted.
So do you know how long
it's been like this?
No, it was like that
when I checked it today.
Who do I complain to about this?
[KYON] It isn't worth
filing a complaint.
[KYON]
Hm?
[KYON growls]
It's weird. Wait, I know,
it's hackers or crackers
or whatever they're called.
No way. It's probably
just an error.
It's so irritating. I can't
believe someone would make
a cyber terrorist attack
on the SOS Brigade!
Oh, when I find out who's
doing this, I'll make 'em do
30 days of community
service, no trial!
[knocking]
Come in.
Well, this is unusual. Miss
Asahina hasn't shown up yet?
[HARUHI] The juniors have more
exams to take, don't they?
[KYON] Hey, everyone, just
hurry up and go home already.
I mean, of all places,
why do you wanna meet here?
Oh, and Haruhi, is there
any special reason
you're not saying anything
about Koizumi knocking?
[KYON] I'm looking forward
to Miss Asahina's tea.
[KYON grunting]
[HARUHI]
That's not it! No, to the right!
[KYON] For a while, I found
myself stuck there catering
to Haruhi's impossible orders.
--[knocking]
--That's not it!
--[HARUHI] Come in.
--[KYON] At last,
the sound of my salvation.
[MIKURU]
Uh, I'm so sorry I'm late.
I had exams until fourth period.
[KYON] With a humble apology,
she appeared, no, descended.
The angel of the
club, Miss Asahina.
Well, I, um... Let's see...
I, um, I sort of brought
a visitor with me.
[KYON] Unbelievable!
I never thought anyone
would come to us for counseling!
But somehow has,
and there she is!
Her name was Emiri Kimidori,
a junior who seemed
very quiet and pure.
So, lemme get this straight.
You want us, the SOS Brigade,
to go and search for
your missing boyfriend?
Yes...
Hm...
Ah.
[sighs]
[KYON] Oh, great.
It seems that she thinks
the purpose of the
SOS Brigade really is to be
a mobile task force or jack-
-of-all-trades counseling-thing.
So, what exactly
is troubling you?
He hasn't been in school
for the longest time.
Have you tried calling him?
He doesn't answer his
cell or his home phone.
I even went to his house,
but he wasn't there.
[HARUHI]
Hm...
What about your
boyfriend's family?
As far as I know,
he lives alone.
A while ago, I remember hearing
they lived and worked overseas,
but I don't have any of
their contact information.
Really? Well, are his
parents in Canada?
No, I believe they live
somewhere in Honduras.
Oh-ho, yes, Honduras! Indeed!
[KYON] What's with this "Indeed"
stuff? I doubt she even knows
where Honduras is.
Let's see, somewhere
below Mexico, right?
That night when I went to see
him, the house was pitch-black.
I'm so worried.
Yeah, I can totally understand
how you're feeling about this.
[KYON]
Liar. You don't understand
the feeling of being in love.
Anyway, I'm surprised you
came to the SOS Brigade
with this mystery.
So why'd you come to us?
My boyfriend used to talk
about the SOS Brigade.
That's why I'm here.
Oh? So who is this boyfriend?
--Ya--
--[cat meows]
is his name.
Don't know him, who's he?
[HARUHI growls]
[KYON]
Hm?
[MIKURU]
To tell you the truth,
he's the president
of the Computer Club.
[KYON]
Hm...
[gasps]
[KYON]
The guy Haruhi took pictures of
as he sexually
harassed Miss Asahina!
The guy Haruhi
blackmailed so she could
take his top-of-
-the-line computer.
The poor guy who was forced
to hook the computer up
with tears in his eyes.
I totally forgot about him.
Okay, I got it. Don't worry,
we'll do something about this.
Miss Kimidori,
today's your lucky day!
Since you're the SOS
Brigade's first client,
I'll solve the case of your
mystery boyfriend for free!
[KYON] You planned on
charging money for this?
Hey.
Taking her case was the easy
part, but what're you gonna do
if you can't solve it?
We'll solve it. I'm sure
the Computer Club chief's
suffering from the May
Melancholies, even if it's
a couple months late.
We'll just stroll into
his house, grab him,
slap him around a little,
and drag him outta there.
[KYON] I think she's serious
about that. But if he's got
a girlfriend like Miss Kimidori,
why's that guy hiding out
in the Computer Club?
Are you and Miss Kimidori
friends or something?
[MIKURU] Mm-mm. I've never
spoken to her before today.
[KYON]
If she needed help,
why didn't she go to a
teacher or the police?
No, maybe she did, but they
didn't take her seriously.
That's why she came to
the SOS Brigade for help.
Yeah, that's what's
going on here.
Looks like Haruhi's using
this as an opportunity
to attract bigger cases.
Bet she can think she
can solve those, too.
We could always pass out flyers
at the front gate
like we did last time.
[KYON] The president
of the Computer Club
lived in a one-room condo.
The building wasn't the best,
but it wasn't the worst.
It was your typical
three-and-a-half story deal,
nothing special.
[HARUHI]
Let's do it.
Well, this is the place.
[HARUHI] But how're we
gonna get in there?
[doorbell rings]
[KYON]
Next time, try that first.
How 'bout if we go up on
the balcony in the back?
Maybe we can get in if we
break the glass or something!
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] The room's on the
third floor, and it's not like
we're a gang of teenage burglars
trying to rob the place.
I don't want a
criminal record yet.
Yeah, okay. Then let's go
down to the manager's office
and borrow the key.
We'll just tell the manager
that we're friends of his
who are worried about him.
[KYON] That excuse is
getting a little old.
[lock clicks]
[KYON] With eyes like liquid
helium, she stared back at me.
You've gotta be kidding.
I didn't realize
it was open. Whatever.
Guess we might as well go in.
He's probably hiding under
the bed or something.
Come on, let's drag
his butt outta there.
[KYON] She doesn't even feel
guilty for swiping that computer
right out of his hands.
Well, that's strange.
I totally thought we'd find him
in a corner of the room
curled up in a ball.
Kyon, do you know where
someone with a case
of the May Melancholies
in July might scurry off to?
[KYON] He's either traveling
in Central or South America,
or he really doesn't
wanna be found.
We should leave now.
[KYON] That's the first
time she's spoken today.
Miss Nagato's right,
we need to go.
[KYON] Don't sound so serious,
don't breathe on me,
you're too close, and
you're freakin' me out.
I'm feeling a little
strange in here.
It's a sensation
--[HARUHI] Awesome!
--I'm all too familiar with,
--Warabi Mochi!
--so we should get going.
It expired three days ago,
but I'm sure they're still good.
Come on, let's eat!
--Say "ah," Mikuru!
--No, don't!
Ah...
What do you mean "familiar"?
It's a familiar scent. This room
has the same kind of smell
as closed space.
[KYON]
Come to think of it,
you're a real life
ESPer, aren't you?
There's another
dimensional layer.
As we stand here,
it's beginning to shift.
[KYON]
Okay, looks like it'd be best
if we all got the
hell out of here.
[MIKURU whimpers]
I am so hungry.
That's it for today. Dismissed!
[KYON]
Hey, wait! What about the case?
Don't worry,
we'll figure it out.
[HARUHI]
See ya!
[KYON]
She's already bored.
Um, is anything the matter?
Why did you want us to come
back here without
telling Miss Suzumiya?
[KYON] Those two seem to
think there's something fishy
with that room.
Isn't that right?
Yes. I'm sure we'll find out
once we get back inside.
Right, Miss Nagato?
[NAGATO] There is a
localized non-corrosive
alternate space in this room.
It's happening independently
in limited mode.
[KYON]
Wow, it almost sounds like
you're just flipping through
a dictionary, pulling
out words at random.
She's saying that
there's something similar
to closed space in here.
It's not the same as the ones
created by Miss Suzumiya.
The one in this
room smells different.
Do you think the disappearance
of the Computer Club President
is related to this space?
Yes.
[gasps]
[indecipherable muttering]
[KYON]
I should've told her to wait.
[gasps]
[KYON]
I couldn't enjoy the feeling
of Mikuru clutching my arm
because I was trying really hard
to figure out where I was.
I remember I was standing
in a small, one-room condo
a second ago, not
this creepy place.
I have analyzed the entry code.
It overlaps standard space.
It is merely out of phase.
[KOIZUMI] This doesn't seem
to be closed space, though.
It's slightly different. In one
segment of this spatial data,
there is junk information
that seems to have originated
with Haruhi Suzumiya.
[KOIZUMI]
Can you tell how much?
Insignificant levels. She only
triggered this situation.
I see, so that's what happened.
[KYON] Can Miss Asahina and I
join this conversation?
So the president of the Computer
Club is somewhere in here?
[KOIZUMI]
It seems that way.
This alternate space
created itself in his room,
and for some reason,
he became trapped within it.
[KYON]
Then where is he?
Wait!
Do you think you can tell me
what you're gonna do first?
I just wanna be
ready for it, okay?
Nothing.
There it is.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
What is that?!
I can definitely
feel its animosity.
[KYON] Those two have ways
of defending themselves,
but Miss Asahina and I
don't even stand a chance!
You wouldn't happen to have...
laser guns or anything?
We're forbidden to carry
firearms because it's dangerous.
[KYON]
Sure, I can understand that.
They wouldn't do her any good
anyway. Besides, she might
accidentally leave it
on the train or something.
Huh...? [gasps]
[KYON] Do you guys know
what camel crickets look like?
For those of you who don't,
I'd like to show you what
I'm looking at right now.
[KYON]
What is this?
[KOIZUMI]
A camel cricket.
[KYON]
Got it. Thanks, Captain Obvious.
[NAGATO] It's the creator
of this dimension.
[KYON]
No way. Did Haruhi do this, too?
[NAGATO] The cause is different,
but she was the catalyst.
[KYON]
Okay, you can move now.
Looks like I can still
access my powers in here.
At least, partially.
But it's only a tenth of
what I usually work with.
Maybe it was determined
that this was all the power
I needed.
[KYON] Yeah, great. Uh,
Nagato, what is that insect
and where is the
Computer Club guy?
It is a data lifeform.
It is currently using the
male student's brain to increase
its probability of survival.
[gasps] Are you saying the
president's inside that thing?
Exactly.
I see... This camel cricket is
a manifestation of the thing
the president fears the most.
If we defeat it, we can shut
down this alternate space.
Am I mistaken?
No mistakes.
Then this should
be relatively easy.
[KYON] Miss Asahina's giving me
a workout. I'm so gonna lose it.
And she's taken away my
mobility so I can't escape.
Don't worry, it'll be over soon.
Just hurry up and do it.
Roger that.
[KOIZUMI grunts]
[KOIZUMI]
Fumoffu!
[KOIZUMI shouts]
Pausing integral seconds
between display.
[KYON]
A force field?!
[KOIZUMI]
Second Wave!
Did that work?
I guess it didn't work.
Is it over now?
[KYON, MIKURU sigh]
[KYON]
Looks like he's still alive.
I suddenly found myself standing
in that one-room condo again.
[NAGATO] It arrived
280 million years ago.
When "it" landed on this planet,
"it" could not find the
necessary means to survive here.
To preserve itself,
"it" went into hibernation.
When humans created
the computer network,
"it" shifted into a
half-wakened state.
Then, an explosion of
unmeasured amounts of data
from a parallel world
caused "it" to fully wake.
[KYON] That explosion of
data from a parallel world
turned out to be the SOS Brigade
logo that Haruhi drew.
That was the trigger.
[NAGATO] In Earth measurements,
this emblem contains
approximately 436
petabytes of data.
[KYON] No way! That thing
isn't more than 100 kilobytes!
[KOIZUMI]
A symbol she happens to draw
turns out to be
something amazing.
Only Miss Suzumiya
could do that.
[KYON] Now I was honestly
starting to get scared.
It can't just be coincidence.
[KYON]
The SOS Brigade is formed
Miss Asahina joins because
she's the perfect mascot.
Koizumi joins because
he's a transfer student.
Nagato joins because she's
been there from the start.
On top of that, Miss Asahina
came from the future,
and Nagato is
sort of... alien-ish.
If all of this really
was Haruhi's doing,
it's just too good to be true.
[KYON] Koizumi says that it's
all because Haruhi wished it,
but I don't believe that.
Look, I'm just an ordinary guy.
And, if it's really true that
everything Haruhi does is
significant in some way,
why did she choose me to become
a member of the SOS Brigade?
Is it because I've got
latent super-crazy powers,
or do I have a secret identity
that no one's told me about?
What in the hell am I, anyway?
[KYON] I know, I'm the
conscious of the SOS Brigade.
I'm here because I have to stop
Haruhi's illegal
club activities.
It's my job to make her have
a normal high school life.
All right, you gotta tell me
what that camel cricket was.
A data lifeform.
Any relation to
your entity thingy?
A similar source. The other
lifeform evolved differently
and its race perished.
[KYON] Or so you thought, until
you found a survivor right here.
Why Earth of all places?
It would've been nice if
it decided to hibernate
on Neptune or something.
To think the internet was the
nursery for an evil overlord-y
thing like that.
[KYON]
Hang on a second.
I just realized, nothing
happened in this room
when Haruhi finished
drawing the logo
And when she showed it to me,
nothing happened then either.
For a while now, this room has
been in an alternate dimension.
Elements and force fields
collide with one another here,
cancelling each other out and
creating a sort of saturation.
But there's no room left for
anything else to blend in.
So, while I wasn't looking,
this room was turned into
an ominous den of weirdness?
Not to worry, I think
it's harmless. Probably...
Oh brother. I really don't
feel like going insane
or looking for a rope
to hang myself with
just because this
place is so strange.
I'm doing my best to make
sure that doesn't happen.
Well, I hope and pray that this
kind of stuff isn't happening
because you're doing your best.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[KYON gasps]
[KYON] There's almost
30,000 hits on this thing!
The data lifeform reproduces
itself by installing
hyperlinks at various locations.
It then copies information
about itself into the brains
of humans who see the emblem
creating more closed space.
[KYON] However, since the
data's become corrupt,
the humans who
saw it most likely
did not suffer a
negative effect.
According to Nagato, there
were eight other idiots
who saw the logo, five of which
were North High students.
Guess this means we have
to go rescue them, too.
[whistle blows]
[COACH] All right, dammit!
Hustle up, take a knee!
[KYON] If you look at it long
enough, the thing actually says
"ZOZ Brigade."
Nagato redid the logo and I
stuck it back onto the page.
The Computer Club guy
came back today.
[HARUHI]
Oh, really?
It was either a case
of the May Melancholies
or an argument with
his girlfriend.
Hey, isn't it amazing though?
Our website's gotten
30,000 hits!
It's like people know a good
thing when they see it.
[KYON]
I wonder...
Could it be that she's the
one who destroyed the data?
And the girl who came
to us, Miss Kimidori,
I asked the Computer Club
chief, and he said
he doesn't have a girlfriend.
Nagato's always been
in the middle of this
elaborate scenario, hasn't she?
[KYON] It wouldn't surprise me
at all if you told me this
omnipotent alien terminal
had done something to
Miss Kimidori, making her
come to us with a case.
Maybe sending a fake
client to us was her way
of getting rid of Haruhi's
boredom for a little while.
I wonder if she's been
doing this the whole time.
Keeping the weirder things
at bay and not saying
anything to anyone.
Quietly, from the shadows...
[KYON] Or maybe... getting
involved with this case
was something that
Nagato wished for.
An android made by aliens
living in an empty room
for years on end.
Nagato... Is it possible
that you get that way, too?
I wonder... Do you feel
lonely when you're alone?