Do you want me to do anything?
Nope, not a thing!
You're good to go.
Huh?
[HARUHI] You can go home now.
We're done for today!
Uh...
[KYON]
You heard what she said.
Our Haruhi-esque activities
are over for the day.
Either through
skilled negotiations
or outright blackmail,
she managed to score
all this stuff.
No money changed hands;
it was 100% free.
There's an old saying:
"There's nothing scarier
than something that's free."
As far as I can tell,
Haruhi isn't afraid of anything.
But if anyone out there knows of
something that would scare her,
give me a shout.
I wanna know what it is.
[TANIGUCHI]
Whatcha got there?
Presents for all
the good little kids?
Yeah, what do ya think?
'Course not.
[TANIGUCHI]
Ha-ho!
Model guns, right on.
Didn't know you were into those.
I'm not, these things
belong to Haruhi.
Ohh... Suzumiya's, huh?
Well, guess it must
be tough for ya.
Huh?
[TANIGUCHI]
That reminds me.
Hm? What's up?
Well, the arts festival
is coming up.
I was just wondering what
you guys were gonna be doing.
What are you asking me for?
Yeah, like I'm definitely
gonna get a serious answer
from Suzumiya.
Nagato doesn't say anything,
so there's no point asking her.
Miss Asahina won't come
anywhere near me,
and the other guy's
kinda creepy, ya know?
I'm outta options,
so that's why I'm asking.
[KYON] Yeah, that's me--
PR guy, nice guy, whatever.
You're definitely
in the latter category.
Huh?
[TANIGUCHI] Well, yeah.
I mean, you're so nice
you'd stick with someone
even if you knew
they were headed straight
for the edge of a cliff.
The typical nice guy.
[KYON growls]
Okay then,
when I find anything out,
you're gonna be
the last to know.
Hey!
[KYON] I already knew
that Haruhi's latest path
to fun and adventure
was gonna lead nowhere.
I didn't need to be
reminded of that.
The thing is, me and Haruhi
weren't the only ones
walking down that path.
There were three others who were
shuffling right along with us.
Now, I didn't have to worry
about two of them;
they'd be okay on their own.
But Miss Asahina wasn't safe.
I mean, you'd think
if she was from the future,
she could predict all the crazy
stuff she gets put through.
[KYON]
But, since that's not the case,
it was up to me to protect her.
[KYON]
Mm-hm.
[HARUHI giggles]
[clock chimes]
[MIKURU screams]
[HARUHI] What? I'm just
helping you get undressed!
Stop struggling!
[MIKURU screams]
[HARUHI]
Come on!
[sighs]
[knocking]
[HARUHI]
Come in!
What the--?!
[MIKURU whimpers]
Well?
[KYON] She looks amazing
in that outfit!
I wonder if it's Kyonic.
Hello, everyone!
Oh, pardon me.
Ooh, wow! That looks
wonderful on you, really!
[KYON]
Yeah, guy, no kidding.
I'm having a hard time
understanding
why we've got a waitress here.
This is a club room, not a cafe.
[HARUHI]
I'll tell you why.
This is the costume
Mikuru's gonna wear
in our awesome movie!
Really?
Won't the maid outfit you make
her put on work just as well?
Of course not!
A maid provides
a more personal service,
usually she's in a
big mansion somewhere.
But waitresses are different.
They work at
restaurants and cafes,
and the services they provide
are for the general public.
Yeah, I know the difference.
But that doesn't explain why
Miss Asahina has to wear that.
Oh, you get so hung up
on the tiny details.
She's dressed like that
because it feels right!
Anyway, I'm cool with it.
[KYON] Okay, but is it
cool with Miss Asahina?
[MIKURU whimpers]
Well, this feels like it might
be a bit too small for me.
I... I can't... I don't...
It's perfect!
The fit's perfect,
you look perfect in it,
everything's perfect!
[KYON]
No use, she's made up her mind.
People! This is gonna be the
concept for our awesome movie!
As the director,
I've dedicated myself to
providing quality
entertainment for the masses!
And when the credits roll,
everyone will be on their feet!
I'm talking standing ovation!
[KYON sighs]
[door clicks]
Huh?
[gasps]
[GROUP]
Uh... Huh?
Yes! Yuki! You totally
understand, don't you?
Yeah! That's it!
[KYON] Not sure what "it" is,
but that has to be
her costume for her class's
fortune-telling thing.
At least, that's what I could
figure out based on the answers
Nagato gave to Haruhi's
rapid-fire questions.
Either way, I wonder
what she was thinking,
walking all the way over here
from class dressed like that.
That costume couldn't
be more perfect
for the character
I have in mind.
How is that supposed
to be perfect?
[HARUHI]
Look!
[KYON]
Hm?
--[KYON gasps]
--[MIKURU yelps]
[gasps]
[KYON]
No way! Is this my fault?
[chuckles]
You're right, it's perfect!
But then I shouldn't
be surprised.
I'd expect nothing less
from you, Miss Suzumiya.
It's wonderful casting.
[KYON] Don't smile at me,
I'll turn to stone.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON]
Yeah, I hear ya.
Okay, Kyon. I want those guns
ready for some action
by the end of the day!
We start shooting tomorrow,
so we'll need 'em.
Oh! And you have to figure out
how to use the camera, too.
Got it?
[KOIZUMI] Do you think there's
going to be trouble?
When have we ever not had any
trouble with her crazy schemes?
Trouble, he says.
Don't make me laugh.
Well, it's not a
laughing matter, per se.
But there's no reason
to worry, either.
How can you be so sure?
The parts she's cast us in are
just characters in her movie.
I seriously doubt Miss Suzumiya
believes I'm a teenage ESPer.
It's just a coincidence.
It's like this:
The Itsuki Koizumi in the movie
is just a character I play.
The fact that he's an
ESPer, too? Again, coincidence.
And if you're worried about her
putting two and two together,
it's hard to believe
anyone would
confuse an actor
with the role they play.
I'm sure some people might,
but I highly doubt
Miss Suzumiya is one of them.
Yeah well, that still doesn't
make me feel better about it.
There's no guarantee that
what you said is the way it is.
[KOIZUMI]
If she was the kind of person
who'd mix reality and fiction,
then you can be pretty sure
our world would be much more
fantastic than it is.
Consider that for a moment,
and you'll see.
Miss Suzumiya is a rational
human being, after all.
[KYON]
A rational human being, he says.
Well, thanks to her
rational god-like ways,
I've had the pleasure
of being dragged head-first
into some of the weirdest
situations of my young life.
Haruhi doesn't even know
what she's capable of.
Of course, we can't
let Miss Suzumiya
find out who we really are.
I'm sure at some point,
we might very well have to
reveal our true
identities to her.
But now is definitely
not the time for it.
Thankfully, Miss Asahina and
Miss Nagato's respective groups
are in agreement with mine.
To be honest,
I wouldn't mind if things
just stayed they way they were.
Then that makes two of us.
I'm not too crazy about
seeing the world go to pieces.
Huh?
If I might make a suggestion,
you should stop worrying
so much about the world.
You should be more
worried about yourself.
If necessary, there are others
who can replace
Miss Nagato and I.
However, there is
no understudy for you.
[KYON]
Hmm.
Man! All this festival crap
pisses me off!
[KUNIKIDA]
Why?
Every time I turn around, I'm
seeing people having a blast.
I'm like the only one
not having any fun.
And seeing all the
couples is the worst.
I'm gonna kill somebody!
[KYON]
Jealousy rears its ugly head.
[TANIGUCHI]
What does our class wanna do?
A freaking survey!
[scoffs] Lame!
If you've got a better idea,
why didn't you say something
when you had the chance?
[KYON]
If you had, maybe Haruhi
wouldn't have come up
with this movie idea.
Yeah! No thanks!
I don't wanna be in charge
of putting it all together!
[KUNIKIDA] Yeah... I wish
Miss Asakura were still here.
She'd do it.
[TANIGUCHI]
I know.
She was double A+!
It really sucks she had
to transfer out of school.
I wonder if it's too late
for me to change classes.
Which one would you wanna go to?
Are you thinkin' about
Miss Nagato's class?
Hang on, I just remembered!
I saw her walkin' around in some
kinda witch costume yesterday.
What was that about?
Yeah, like I'd know. Sorry, pal.
[TANIGUCHI]
I just remembered!
That time I walked in
on you and her
all tangled up on
the classroom floor.
That was nothing.
Yeah, I know.
It was just something
Suzumiya cooked up
or something, right?
Huh?
Oh... Yeah...
[KYON] Taniguchi's complete
and utter misunderstanding
of that day gave me some relief.
Thanks, Taniguchi. Your
stupidity will save the world.
[TANIGUCHI]
Man... This is boring...
[HARUHI] Okay, people!
Let's shoot a movie!
This is sudden.
I looked all over the school
for a good location.
But nothing worked, so we'll
have to find some place else.
--Come on, Mikuru! Get ready!
--[MIKURU whimpers]
Um, do I really have to go too?
[HARUHI]
Well, yeah...
We can't shoot anything
without our lead actress!
Uh, okay, but... do I
have to wear this outside?
[HARUHI]
You sure do!
[MIKURU] Can't I at least
wear a jacket over this?
[HARUHI]
No! The more you think about it,
the more nervous
you're gonna get.
How do you expect
to win the Golden Globe
if you're behaving like this?
[KYON]
I thought we were trying to be
the #1 event of the
festival or something.
[HARUHI]
Oh, yeah! Yuki!
Here! Hang onto this!
I changed your character
into an evil alien witch.
So, what do you think?
[KYON] She's already
rewriting the script!
I guess Nagato's powers could
be considered magical, though.
[HARUHI] Come on, Kyon!
Get the camera ready!
Right! Let's shoot a movie!
Here we go!
[KYON] God help us.
She looks like she's serious.
[HARUHI singing]
Huh?! The heck's that?!
Hey, Haruhi, wait a sec.
[HARUHI]
Hm?
It's just... I don't think
it's a good idea
for these two to get on
the train dressed like this.
I don't see
anything wrong with it.
There definitely is!
Uh-uh! If they were butt-naked,
then yeah, they'd get arrested,
but they're both
wearing clothes.
Or maybe, you'd prefer
the bunny-girl outfit!
Oh, you shoulda said so earlier.
[KYON]
After going to all the trouble
to find this waitress costume,
I'm shocked to
hear you say that!
Wait, didn't you say
her being a waitress
was part of the concept?
Right now, what's important is
your ability to
adapt to the situation.
Adaptability is how all life on
this planet evolved, right?
And if you don't evolve,
you're gonna get left behind.
[KYON] Then if the
planet were sentient,
it would have chucked Haruhi
way out into space by now.
[train screeches]
[HARUHI]
Look! The train's here!
Come on, Mikuru! Stop stalling!
[MIKURU sobs]
[HARUHI]
Hey, there! We're here!
[SHOPKEEPER]
Oh, and right on time, I see.
Is this the same girl
from yesterday?
I didn't recognize her.
[laughs]
[SHOPKEEPER]
Okay then, you better get to it!
Just leave everything to us!
All right, people!
We're gonna have a quick
meeting, so gather 'round.
Here's the deal,
we're gonna shoot a commercial!
[ALL]
Huh?
[giggling]
Hi... Um, this store is neat,
and the owner's a really
friendly person, too...
H-He's a really nice guy, too!
And, um, they've been
in business a long time,
ever since Mr. Eijiro's
grandpa opened it.
It's all right here,
from batteries to refrigerators,
they have it all!
And, um... Anyway, come on down
to Ohmori Electronics,
where good deals
are made every day!
[HARUHI]
Okay! Cut it!
I'm just not feeling
the emotion in this scene.
The vibe's all wrong, but I'm
not sure how to tweak it.
[CHILD]
Mama, what's that?
[PASSERBY]
Shh, those are crazy people.
[gasps] I've got it!
[KYON]
Oh, for the love of God,
please don't "get"
anything else!
A waitress doesn't belong
outside an electronics store!
[KYON]
That's what you "got"?!
Gimme that small bag
over there, Koizumi. I need it.
[KOIZUMI]
Right.
[KYON] "Give me a camera
and I'll put a commercial
for your store
in the middle of the movie!"
"Sounds good!"
That's the conversation
Haruhi and the owner had.
Cut down to
five seconds, though.
[HARUHI]
C'mere, Mikuru!
What a relief!
Doesn't look like I'm gonna
get any lines in this today.
[KYON]
Hm?
You see, I'm also
supposed to be acting
in my class's stage production
for the arts festival.
Thing is, I've having a little
trouble remembering my lines.
You don't say...
I'd actually prefer it if the
role I'm playing in the movie
didn't have too much dialogue.
I know! What if you took over
the lead role for me?
Haruhi's the one to talk to
about the casting decisions.
If you want to switch with me,
you should probably talk to her.
Do you honestly think
I'm capable of
doing something so frightening?
After all, these are
Miss Suzumiya's orders.
Imagine the consequences
if I disobeyed her.
That's something
I don't wanna think about.
That makes two of us then.
Now you know why
I'm just standing here,
biting my lip
and running the camera.
[HARUHI]
We're back!
[gasps]
[KYON]
Whoa!
It's the return of Miss
Asahina's greatest costume ever!
The flawless bunny girl!
[sighs]
Last time I saw her
in that was six months ago.
So much has happened since then.
Looking back, they're all
such fond memories now.
Yeah! Like hell they are!
[HARUHI]
Okay! Now that's much better!
There's nothing like a hot
bunny girl to sell a product!
Get ready! We're gonna
take it from the top!
Kyon, fire up the camera.
[HARUHI]
Take two's up!
[beep]
[HARUHI giggling]
[KYON] Anyway,
we wrapped the commercial
for the electronics store.
Our day wasn't over though.
If you recall, there was
another sponsor we visited.
We were trudging
over there right now.
[HARUHI]
Okay, Mikuru, you ready?
Do it just like before.
There wasn't anything wrong
with your performance.
[KYON]
Everything was wrong with it!
And... action!
[beep]
Ah... I'm standing here in front
of Keiji Yamatsuchi's
Model Shop.
He opened it last year
after quitting his
dead-end corporate job!
And... models were his hobby,
so he figured
why not open a store?
Unfortunately, his sales
have been down for a while...
And... compared to last year,
his first-half earnings for this
year are down about 80%...
And so, everyone should
come down here
and buy lots of models!
Thank you!
[sighs]
Huh? You want me to hold it?
[MIKURU]
Y-You should never shoot this
while pointing it
at other people.
You should only shoot
empty cans with it.
Huh? You want me to shoot?
--[gunshots]
--[MIKURU wailing]
And... cut it!
[HARUHI] Not too shabby
for a day of shooting.
But get ready 'cause tomorrow,
we start on the movie!
We've already got 15 minutes
worth of commercials
in the camera.
How long is this movie
supposed to be?!
We'll just shoot as
much footage as we can,
and then figure it out
when we edit.
Cutting it together on the
computer should be a snap!
[KYON] And who's gonna be
doing all this "snapping"?
I have a feeling "editor"
was one of the jobs
that was listed under my name.
Tomorrow's Saturday
and there's no school,
so I want everyone
to show up on time.
We'll meet at
Kitaguchi Station at 9 am.
Hang on a sec, Haruhi.
Don't you think you should maybe
do something about
Miss Asahina's costume?
There's gotta be something
else should could wear
that's a little more...
appropriate for fighting.
Maybe something like a
plugsuit or a stealth suit.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Then there would be no surprise
when she actually
started fighting!
I want the audience to freak out
when this timid little
waitress starts kicking butt!
It gets their attention!
That's what a
concept's all about!
[KYON]
I wonder if she even understands
the meaning of
the word "concept."
Thanks for explaining
what a concept's about.
We all know she's
from the future,
but why's it so
important to the story?
Uh... That is--I--
I mean her character!
Her character doesn't have
to be from the future, does she?
[HARUHI]
Don't worry.
Those are details
we can figure out
when we get to that
point in the story.
And, if we can't
figure something out,
we just ignore it.
As long as it's entertaining,
it's gonna be cool!
[growls]
But for that to work,
it's gotta be entertaining
in the first place!
There's no point in making this
if you're the only
being entertained!
Are you trying to
get a Golden Raspberry
for amateur film-making?!
Are you kidding?
We've only got one goal:
To be the #1 event in
the arts festival this year.
And after that, we're aimin'
for the Golden Globes, too!
Show me the script then.
I wanna see how
it's coming along.
[gasps]
Don't worry about that.
I've got all that stuff
right up here.
The script and the
storyboards are done,
and they're all ready to go!
See?
You don't have
to do any thinking!
If that's the way you want it.
[KYON] You don't have
to do any thinking either.
Sit and stare out
the window for all I care.
You could be as cute
as Miss Asahina
if you could just figure out
how to be more
pleasant to deal with.
Hm? What?
It's nothing.
Okay, guys, let's get
fired up for tomorrow!
The only way to grab the glory
is to have a positive attitude!
When you free yourself from
the stuff that holds you back,
your hidden strengths
will be revealed!
Then, you'll be able to tap
into unimaginable powers!
[KYON] You sound like
a character in a manga
unleashing a counter-attack.
[CHILD]
Look! It's a balloon!
[KYON]
The next day,
we were about to find
ourselves thrown into
the middle of some totally
bizarre situation that--
Wait, I lost my
train of thought.
What did Haruhi say again?
Something like,
"When you free yourself from
the stuff that's
holding you back,
your hidden strengths
will be revealed,
and you'll tap into
unimaginable powers."
[KYON sighs]
Yeah, but Haruhi, you did it.
You have that kind of power.
You just can't ever
find out about it.
You're late again!
It's not even 9:00 yet.
You're the last to show up.
As punishment,
you're gonna pay for lunch!
Yeah, whatever.
I have decided to cover
everyone's bus fare.
It's a necessary expense.
[KYON sighs]
Thank you.
Oh, yeah! I need to put this on!
[KYON]
Huh?
You're wearing your
uniform on Saturdays now?
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
She told me yesterday
I had to wear it.
It's for my part.
Since I'm supposed
to be an ESPer
disguised as an ordinary
high school student,
the uniform is essential
to the character.
[KYON]
So you're just playing yourself.
[HARUHI]
There, that should do it.
Okay, guys,
the bus stop's over there!
Come on, Kyon! Hurry up!
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[KYON] After half an hour of
rattling around on a bus,
and another half
hour of walking,
we ended up at a location that
could only be described as...
...the place where
no one ever goes.
Man, it's hot. It's hot.
[MIKURU]
Um...
Would you like some?
I hope you don't mind,
I drank out of it first.
Thanks! I'll totally have some!
[gasps]
You can have a
drink later, got it?
That goes for you, too!
You don't have time
to be givin' the PAs a drink
when we've got
so much work to do today!
As soon as the camera
comes out, we shoot!
Get changed!
[whimpers]
But I--
No one's gonna see you...
Just go behind
a tree or something!
Uh, thank you!
Hey, no peeking!
I wouldn't dare.
Ta-da!
It's a colored contact!
It's super important for
any self-respecting heroine
to have different colored eyes.
If one eye's different,
it enhances the
character's mystique!
Besides, it's symbolic,
so there!
It's all about the
secret behind her blue eye!
Okay... But it wouldn't
really make sense
if her eyes were different
colors for no reason, right?
So, what's the secret?
It's still a secret!
[KYON]
Huh?
Come on, Mikuru. Now's not the
time for you to get cold feet!
[HARUHI]
Oh, come on, Mikuru!
Don't be so shy, keep running!
Get into the character!
Become the heroine!
Let's try it one more time
from the top, okay?
Huh?
[whimpering]
[KYON] So... It looks like this
is our opening sequence, folks.
I was expecting to see a script
or at least a treatment by now.
But Haruhi said
there wasn't gonna be one.
If I wrote it down
and it got leaked,
it would be the
worst thing ever!
[KYON]
That's the reason she gave.
I wonder when this turned
into a Hong Kong production.
Okay! Hit me one more time!
Just like you did in take three!
[MIKURU whines]
[HARUHI] Next up,
we got the fight scene
between Mikuru and Yuki!
Mikuru, empty your clips
into Yuki, okay?
What? But I thought
you weren't supposed to
shoot anyone with these.
No, it's okay!
I doubt that you're even gonna
hit her, so just fire away!
Besides, Yuki can
dodge the pellets
if they get too close to her!
Go on.
Shoot me.
[HARUHI]
See? She's cool with it!
Light her up!
Oh, but don't fire them
at the same time.
Alternate. It's the basic
technique of two-gun shoot-outs!
[MIKURU whimpering]
--[pellets firing]
--[MIKURU whimpering]
Yeah, sure,
I guess that'll work.
[KYON sighs]
Can I say something?
This doesn't seem like a movie.
I have no idea
what's going on or anything.
Don't worry.
It'll all come
together in editing
after a little cutting
and pasting, you'll see.
And who's gonna be doing all
this "cutting and pasting," huh?
You could at least put
some dialogue in the movie.
It's okay.
We'll take out the sound
and stick the dialogue in later.
I wanna put in some cool sound
effects and music anyway.
Don't think so hard,
just go with the flow.
[sighs]
[KYON] Yeah, well, since
the story's all in your head,
I guess there's nothing
for us to think about...
...even if we wanted to.