[KYON]
It was the day after Obon.
Smackdab in the
middle of summer.
Nothing special.
Just an ordinary day.
[KYON] The game on TV
was between schools
from another town.
I had nothing to do
with either school,
but because I tend to
sympothize with underdogs,
I found myself routing
for the losing team.
And that's right about the time
my cell phone started ringing.
[phone ringing]
[KYON]
Haruhi.
[HARUHI]
Hey, you're free, right?
Good, then meet us at 2:00
in front of the station.
But I--!
--[beeping]
--[KYON groans]
[KYON] And just like
that, she hangs up.
How does she know I'm not
doing anything today?
I mean, I could be.
Yeah, I know, I'm
not doing anything,
but still...
--[KYON] Hm?
--[phone ringing]
[KYON]
What?
[HARUHI]
I forgot to tell you something.
Bring your swim trunks.
And your bike, too.
Oh, and money! Bring money.
That's it! Over and out!
[KYON]
Uh. No.
What was that all about?
[KYON'S SISTER]
Hm?
[COMMENTATOR] ...rounding
third on his way home.
And there's Suzuki on the mound.
He is not having a good day.
You gotta feel bad for that guy.
Oh, that is tragic.
He looks like...
[KYON sighs]
[KYON]
Oh, well.
[COMMENTATOR]
Even the fans are quiet.
They're not even
booing Suzuki anymore.
So, with that, the score
is now eight, zero.
Kuyamoto's really got their
work cut out for 'em.
You're late, Kyon! Penalty!
You have absolutely no
motivation whatsoever.
How dare you keep your
brigade leader waiting!
You're gettin' a
penalty for this!
[KYON]
I'm here 15 minutes early.
How come I'm still
the last one to arrive?
[HARUHI] Okay, now that we're
all present and accounted for,
we can go.
Koizumi, you're gonna
have to give Mikuru
a ride over there, okay?
[MIKURU]
Hm?
Yuki and me'll hop on
the back of Kyon's bike.
Do you mind if I ask
where we're going today?
[HARUHI growls]
To the public pool,
where do you think?
We've got lots and lots of
summer vacation-y things to do
during our summer break.
We've only got so much time,
and once it's gone,
it's gone for good, ya know?
So we're gonne do everything
we can while we can
during our one and only
summer as tenth graders.
[KYON]
Once it's gone, it's gone, huh?
[HARUHI sniffing]
Can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes it
feel like summer.
Woohoo!
Let's go! Ha, ha!
Hurry up and get in, guys!
The water's warm. It's perfect!
[KYON] Can't she see
the no diving signs?
I mean, they're everywhere.
It kind of makes
me smile, though.
I mean, to see Miss Suzumiya
enjoying herself
in a normal way.
It's rather charming, isn't it?
She called me outta the blue,
ran down a list of
things to bring,
and ordered me to meet her
without telling me
what was going on.
Yeah, there's nothing
charming or normal about it.
[KOIZUMI] Well, as long as Miss
Suzumiya's having a good time,
we don't have to worry about
any earth-shattering events.
Man, I hope you're right.
Hm. I don't think you
need to worry about it.
I mean, there haven't
been any problems
since our outing
a few weeks ago.
And right now, as far as
Miss Suzumiya's concerned,
and as far as we're concerned,
the world is at peace.
[KYON]
Hm.
[HARUHI]
Okay, guys, lunch time!
And, surprise, surprise!
Mikuru's made us sandwiches!
[KYON]
Whoa.
It's delicious.
Thank you very much!
I'm gonna have another
piece of fried chicken!
Pour some tea, Mikuru.
[MIKURU]
Okay.
[KYON] Things do seem
peaceful, that's for sure.
[CHILDREN]
We're sorry!
[HARUHI]
Yeah, here I come!
[KYON] Now I know why they call
it a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone
in town's here today.
[whimpering, yelps]
Oh, some on, Mikuru!
You're supposed to catch it!
[KYON] This isn't a bad way
to spend a summer vacation.
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
[KYON]
Hm?
These two guys are
my brigade members.
They do what I say,
so if you want somethin',
you can ask them.
[CHILDREN]
Okay!
[sighs]
[HARUHI] I had a couple ideas
about the rest of our vacation.
Check it out!
[KYON]
What's that thing?
it's a schedule of all the
things the brigade's gonna do
before our vacation ends!
[KYON]
The SOS brigade?
You know it! We've only got two
more weeks of vacation left,
right, guys?
But it still feels like
there's a lotta things left
for us to do.
I say we gotta pick up the pace.
So, you made a schedule
of things to do
before our vacation ends, huh?
Go on a trip, go to the
pool, to a Bon fesitval,
see fireworks, part
time job, stargazing--
that's a lotta stuff.
[KYON] And she expects us to do
all this in the next two weeks?
Great.
Can you think of anything
else you wanna do?
[MIKURU]
Um...
I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay! Then goldfish
scooping it is.
We'll start on
the list tomorrow.
Does anyone know if
there's a Bon festival
happening some place close by?
Or if there's a firework show?
[KYON] Why don't you look
this stuff up yourself?
I'll check around and
try to find something.
I'll call you if I do, okay?
[HARUHI] Oh, and don't forget
about the goldfish scooping.
It's Mikuru's only request.
[KOIZUMI]
Got it!
[KYON] How come I always
get stuck with the check?
Becase you were
late, that's why!
And don't you make
us wait tomorrow!
That's it. See ya!
Awesome.
Looks like we're gonna be
running around everyday, now.
[phone ringing]
[KYON] The next morning, I was
waken from my peaceful slumber
by a call from Haruhi.
[KYON] She said they'd
found a Bon festival,
and it was happening tonight.
At a park somewhere.
Well, that was fast.
And convenient.
I was just beginning
to appreciate that fact
when Haruhi suddenly said...
We're all gonna go out
and buy yukatas!
Yuki doesn't have one
and neither does Mikuru.
But I know a place that
sells 'em cheap, so, let's go!
[KYON] Haruhi picked out yukatas
for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then, headed for
the changing rooms.
This was gonna take a while.
[KYON] After about an
hour of standing there
and getting strange
looks from people,
the girls finally decided to
come out of the changing room.
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
[BOTH gasp]
[KYON]
Whoa.
You all look really wonderful
in them. I mean it.
[HARUHI] Of course we do!
I picked them out myself.
Especially Mikuru's.
Look at you, you're
so cute. I'm a genius!
I have awesome fashion
sense, don't'cha think?
[HARUHI giggles]
[KYON] Of all the costumes
Haruhi has forced her to wear,
this had to be
the best one yet.
She looks awesome.
Yes, she does.
I always wondered what
it would be like
to wear traditional
Japanese clothing.
It's a little tight around
the chest, but it's beautiful.
We're ready to go!
And now it's off to the Bon
festival to have some fun!
A Bon festival, huh?
I haven't been to one of these
things in a really long time.
[gasps] Look, Mikuru!
They've got goldfish scooping,
just like you wanted!
I bet you're gonna catch a ton!
Don't forget the black
demikens are worth 200 points!
Do you wanna go
scoop some fish, too?
We could have a contest to
see how many we can catch.
I think I'll pass.
Besides, I'm more interested
in the food around here.
How 'bout you, Nagato?
Do you wanna get some food?
Are you actually
into that stuff?
[NAGATO]
That.
Hm? It's yours for 800 yen!
[HARUHI]
Thirteen!
I caught a whole bunch,
but I only kept one
'cause I don't have any
place to keep all of 'em.
I tried, but I couldn't catch
a single one of them.
Scooping them up is a lot
harder then it looks, huh?
Yeah, well, it's rare for anyone
to catch a lot, let alone one.
If you can figure out
the trick, it's easy!
Huh?
What's with the mask
you've got there, Yuki?
I bought it.
[HARUHI]
I know, but why that one?
Maybe she felt some kinda
connection to it, or something.
[KYON]
Cause she's an alien.
[HARUHI]
Huh.
Well, okay then.
Anyway, there's a ton of stuff
over there we haven't seen!
You still in fun mode?
Of course! Come on! Hurry up!
--[HARUHI] Here.
--[KYON] Hm?
Go ahead and have one,
but only one, 'kay?
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Pretty good, huh?
[KYON]
Mm-hm.
You know it.
Okay, we've seen just about
everything there is to see.
So now we're gonna go
shoot off some fireworks.
Really? Fireworks?
We went to all the
trouble of dressing up,
so we'll end our day
with a firework show.
Why not? There's a booth over
there that's selling them.
Let's go down by the river bank.
[KOIZUMI]
This is going to be so much fun.
[HARUHI]
Come on! Let's do this!
[laughing]
Kakizaki!
[HARUHI laughing]
[giggles] It's pretty.
So, we did the
Bon festival, fireworks.
That's two down.
And tomorrow, we're gonna
go catch some bugs.
Uh, Haruhi, I don't wanna
spoil your fun or anything,
but have you finished
your summer homework?
[KYON] I should talk.
I haven't even touched mine.
Are you kidding? That
stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it all
in about three days.
Huh?!
Yeah, I finished doing all
of my homework in July.
Ya have to get rid
of that junk first
so you can spend the rest
of your summer having fun
and not worrying about it.
That's the only way to really
get the most out
of your vacation.
[KYON] Why does she
have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs
weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying
up the stats for us.
So anyway, we're gonna go
bug catching tomorrow.
And the prize for catching
the most bugs is gonna be...
Hm...
The winner gets to be brigade
leader for a whole day!
[KYON]
No thank you.
That sounds like fun.
But can we catch just
any random bug?
[HARUHI]
Hm... No.
Only cicadas!
That's it!
I'm calling it the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest!
Whoever catches the
most cicadas wins!
--[KYON groans]
--[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON] The next day,
I wanted it to rain so bad,
I drove a nail through
a teruteru bouzu.
But, despite my efforts,
the day was clear and beautiful.
It was the warmest day
of summer so far,
and all the cicadas were
happy because of it.
I wonder if anyone's ever
tried eating a cicada...
[KYON]
No idea.
They could be good
fried in tempura.
[KYON]
Bon appetit.
I always wondered about food
that's deep-fried in tempura.
Maybe the batter they use
is what makes everything
taste so good.
'Cause then cicadas
would taste great!
[KYON] Apologize to the
tempura chefs! Do it!
Ahem. What's wrong
with this picture?
High schoolers carrying nets
and little plastic boxes?
Hello? What're you thinking
making us hike
all the way up here
carrying all this stuff?
What're you talking about?
If we didn't have
the nets and the bins,
we wouldn't be able
to catch cicadas.
[KYON] That's not the point
I was trying to make.
Okay. Let's go hunting.
Remember, winner gets to be
brigade leader for a day.
Ya ready? Go!
[KYON]
Ignored.
She looks determined
to win, doesn't she?
And that would be a good
thing, don't you think?
[KYON] Jeez. I haven't done
this since elementary school.
I know, me too.
Come on. Let's go have some fun.
[sighs]
[KYON]
What's that? You catch one?
Yeah, no. That's not a cicada.
Oh.
[KYON gasps]
A Hercules beetle?!
[HARUHI]
Let's tally 'em up!
Mikuru caught one.
Yuki caught four.
Koizumi caught seven.
Kyon caught nine.
But the one who
caught the most is...
[KYON]
Don't say it, we already know.
[HARUHI]
Me, with 12!
I guess I just can't give up
being brigade leader,
even for one day.
Sorry about that, you guys.
Please tell me that
you're not gonna
batter those things up
in tempura and fry them.
What? Do you really
wanna eat 'em?
No, I don't wanna eat 'em.
Just kidding.
It's important to
follow the spirit
of catch and release
with these guys.
You never know.
If we let them go now,
they might return
the favor some time.
Hurry!
Go back to the mountains and
try not to get caught anymore!
[KYON]
Wait. No.
You act like you
did a good deed,
but all you did was catch 'em
and let 'em go. Come on.
So, the day after our bug hunt,
Haruhi was kind enough
to get us part-time jobs
at a local supermarket
that really needed the help.
See, they were
having a big sale.
Well, don't work too hard, okay?
[KYON] And our job was
to attract cu
[MIKURU]
Thank you for coming.
[KOIZUMI]
Balloon? No?
[NAGATO]
Here.
--[KYON yelps]
--[KID laughs]
[KYON] Can someone please
tell me why I have to wear
this unbearably hot costume?
Part-time job?
She could've found something
a little more
appropriate for summer.
Look at her.
All cool and breezy.
I swear. If she gets more
money then us, I'm gonna riot.
[MIKURU groaning]
Now I know how a snake feels
when it sheds its skin.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
That's a clever way
of putting it.
Knock, knock.
The manager's super grateful
for all the hard work you did.
Who cares how grateful
he is. What about our pay?
[HARUHI]
This is it.
[KYON]
Huh?
This cool frog
costume is our pay.
Can't tell ya how long
I've had my eye on him.
The manager said
we could have it
'cause he thought Mikuru
looked so darn cute in it.
We'll keep him in the clubroom
as a souvenir of today.
Mikuru, you have my
permission to wear him
whenever you want, okay?
Isn't it great?
--[MIKURU whines]
--[KYON] Ribbit.
[KYON] The pool, the Bon
festival, bug catching,
and a part-time job.
Next on Haruhi's
schedule, stargazing.
Wow, that's what a telescope
from this time frame looks like?
It doesn't seem too different
from the ones in Kepler's time.
[KYON]
Yeah, no. It's pretty different.
[MIKURU] Did you buy
this just for tonight?
Oh, no. Astronomy
was sort of a hobby of mine
when I was younger.
All it took was a glimpse
of the moons of Jupiter,
and after that, I was hooked.
[KYON]
Hm?
[KOIZUMI]
I've found Mars. Have a look.
[HARUHI]
I wonder if they're real.
[KYON]
What's real?
Martians, of course!
[KYON]
I kind of hope they aren't.
I mean, octopoid-like monsters,
wriggling around,
plotting to take
over the planet?
Nothing about that
sounds appealing to me.
Oh, what do you know.
And who cares what
they look like anyway.
They might be friendly.
For all we know,
they could be a
reserved race of beings
living in underground
caves. Think of that.
Whoever they are,
I'm sure they're just trying
not to scare us earthlings.
[KYON]
The martians in your imagination
sound unbelievably boring.
[HARUHI]
I've had enough of Mars.
Let's look for UFOs.
On a night like tonight,
I bet there's some kinda alien
scouting fleet up there.
All right, come on, Mikuru.
Help me with this.
[MIKURU]
Uhh... UFO. UFO...
[HARUHI chuckling]
[MIKURU]
Uh...
[KYON]
Our summer vacation continues.
And the next thing
Haruhi said was...
We're going to the
batting cages today!
[KYON]
Why there?
I was watching a high school
baseball game this morning,
and then it hit me!
Why should we settle for
baseball in some sandlot?
What we need to do is
turn the SOS brigade
into a national league team!
[MIKURU whimpers, yelps]
[KYON]
Chuka soba!
She sure is something.
Where does she get
her energy from?
I bet she's got
special mitochondria
packed in her cells.
More than the
average person, anyway.
If only she'd use
her gifts for good.
[HARUHI yells]
[KYON]
After that, we kept going.
Haruhi was determined to stick
to the schedule she made.
So we were constantly on
the move, day after day,
with no time to hit pause.
We went to a real firework show.
The fireworks burst into bloom
in the sky, one after another,
leaving us with a grand
feeling in our hearts.
And on another day,
she made all of us
enter a goby fishing
tournament down by the river.
[MIKURU screaming]
[HARUHI]
Oh! Mikuru, your pole!
[KOIZUMI] Don't worry,
I see it. I'll go get it.
[KYON] And still, another day
was the the "test of courage."
It's a summertime must,
but I doubt anyone
really does it anymore.
[KYON] Then we went and saw this
over-hyped summer blockbuster.
Turned out to be the
same old, same old.
[KYON]
We went to the beach.
Right in the middle
of jellyfish season.
[KYON]
Then, bowling.
But, you-know-who made a rule
where no one could leave
until everyone got a strike.
Then, an excruciating
karaoke session
designed to push our
vocal cords to the limit.
[KYON] Sure, there were a couple
of non-summertime things
that slipped in,
but looking back,
I can honestly say we had
the time of our lives.
The past two weeks were a blast.
[HARUHI] I declare that
on this day, August 30th,
we've done everything
on our list.
[KYON]
And no one died in the process.
[HARUHI]
Hm...
But now I wonder
if we did enough.
Maybe if we--No, I guess
we did do everything.
Unless there's something else
you guys wanted to do.
No, not really.
I think we've done enough.
I think I'd like to
sleep for a while.
How 'bout you?
Oh.
Oh, well. That's cool.
We did just about everything
we wanted to do this summer.
We wore yukatas, and
caught a lotta cicadas.
We went all over the place.
I guess that's about it, huh?
[KYON]
Please don't tell me there's
something else she wants to do.
[HARUHI]
Okay, we're done for today.
I set tomorrow aside,
just in case,
but you can just
take the day off.
[HARUHI] I'll see everyone
at the clubroom on Monday.
[groans]
I still haven't done
any of my homework.
[KYON] August 31st.
The last day of vacation.
No matter how hard I tried,
I wasn't gonna
finish my homework.
Besides, I was still recovering
from all that running around.
So, I made a decision to
spend the rest of the day
in lounge mode.
[MAN]
What the heck?!
[KYON]
Boring.
Uh...
[KYON]
Homework? Yeah, whatever.
[yawns]
[sighs]
I guess I'll go to bed now.
I got school tomorrow.
Beep.