[KYON]
Wrong...
Wrong.
Wrong!
Something's wrong.
That's what it felt like anyway.
The game on TV was between
schools from another town.
Now I had nothing to
do with either school,
but I found myself rooting for
the losing team anyway.
And it was right about then,
I suddenly got the feeling
Haruhi was gonna call.
[phone rings]
Hey Kyon, your phone's ringing.
I know; you don't
have to tell me.
[phone rings]
[sighs]
[HARUHI]
Hey, you're free, right? Good.
Meet us at 2:00 in front of
the station. And don't be late!
[dial tone]
[KYON] I didn't even have
a chance to say anything.
[phone rings]
[gasps]
Yeah, what?
[HARUHI]
I forgot to tell you,
make sure to bring your swim
trunks and lots of money.
Oh, and bring your bike.
Definitely bring your bike.
I guess that's it. Over and out!
[dial tone]
[KYON]
That's two for two.
[sighs]
[KYON]
That was weird.
It was like I knew what
Haruhi was gonna say
before she said it.
Yeah... No...
Actually, it felt like we'd had
that exact same conversation
once before, kinda like
déjà vu or something.
--[metal clink]
--[cheering]
[COMMENTATOR]
Ooh, what a shot!
It's a big, fat hit headin'
straight for left field!
And it is over
the fence! Home run!
Chalk up another run for Jonah.
That makes eight
so far this game.
Kashima rounding third...
[KYON]
Summer's almost over...
[HARUHI]
You're late, Kyon!
Where's your motivation, huh?
[KYON]
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry to keep you
guys waiting for me.
No worries,
I just got here, too!
Okay, now that we're all present
and accounted for, we can go!
Where to?
To the public swimming pool.
Where do ya think?
[KYON] That figures...
considering the stuff I brought.
We've got lots of summer
vacation-y things
to do during our summer break!
But we've only so
much time because
once it's gone,
it's gone for good!
So we're gonna do everything
we can, while we can,
during our only summer
as tenth graders!
And for starters, we're gonna
ride the bikes to the pool!
[KYON] Okay, but did everyone
ride their bikes?
No, the only bikes we have today
are the ones you and I brought.
Huh?
All right, Kyon, you can't
let Koizumi beat you!
Come on! Full speed ahead!
[KYON panting]
Why's it takin' so long,
you guys?
Hurry up and park
the bikes already!
Hm?
Seriously, Kyon, we're
tryin' to have fun here,
so stop acting tired.
[KYON]
Whose fault is that, huh?!
[HARUHI]
Aah, can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes
it feel like summer!
Come on, let's go for a swim!
You and me are
gonna have a race!
[MIKURU]
Miss Suzumiya, wait!
[HARUHI screams, laughs]
[water splashes]
Doesn't that look like fun?
Sure does.
[KOIZUMI]
In a way, it makes me smile.
It's such a peaceful scene,
don't you think?
I mean, look at them.
Seein' Miss Suzumiya enjoy
the day in a normal fashion,
it's charming, isn't it?
Well, she called me up
and told me what to bring.
Then, she demanded I meet her
without telling me
what was going on.
There's nothing charming
or normal about it.
Well, if you want my opinion,
none of what you said is
anything to make a fuss over.
I mean, as long as Miss
Suzumiya's laughing
and havin' a good time,
we don't have to worry about any
earth-shattering events, do we?
[KYON]
Man, I hope you're right.
[KOIZUMI gasps]
Something wrong?
Nothing...
[chuckles]
Just my imagination, I guess.
With everything that's
happened since we met,
you could say I've become
slightly paranoid.
[gasps]
Oh! I lost again!
Yuki, one more time! Come on!
[MIKURU gasping]
[screams]
[laughing]
I'm comin' to get you!
[HARUHI mumbling]
Mikuru! This is delicious!
[KYON]
Geez...
Now I know why they call it
a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone
in town's here today.
I wonder why Haruhi
chose this place.
Hm?
[KYON]
Geez...
Now I know why they call it
a "public" swimming pool.
Seems like everyone
in town's here today.
I wonder why Haruhi
chose this place.
Hm?
[KYON gasps]
Something weird's happening...
[KYON]
Yeah... That's right.
She shows up and says...
[BOTH] "These two guys
are my brigade members.
They do what I say,
so if you want something,
you can ask them!"
It's time for some fun!
Let's go play water soccer!
Yeah, we're coming.
[KYON] Oh, well.
Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
[KYON]
What... is that?
I came up with this schedule of
how we're gonna spend the
rest of our summer vacation!
I realized something...
We've only got two more weeks
of summer vacation left to go!
So, we're gonna start
pickin' up the pace!
[KYON]
Two weeks to do all that?!
Mikuru, is there anything
else you wanna do?
[MIKURU]
Hm?
Um...
I think I'd like to try
goldfish scooping.
Okay!
Goldfish... scooping... it is!
Perfect!
Pardon me, but could I
see that for a moment?
Okay, sure...
Thank you.
Oh, you done with it?
[KOIZUMI]
Mhm.
[HARUHI] Okay, then we
start the list tomorrow!
Does anyone know if there's a
bon festival happening anywhere?
Or a place where we
can see fireworks?
[KOIZUMI]
I can check around for those.
Don't forget about
the goldfish scooping!
[MIKURU laughs nervously]
[KOIZUMI]
I'll get right on it.
[KYON]
Stuck with the bill again.
Well, that's it for today!
See ya!
[KOIZUMI]
I'm off, too.
[MIKURU]
I'll see you later.
[KYON]
Nagato!
Uh... It's nothing important
or anything...
So how've you been?
Is everything okay?
It is.
That's good to hear.
Yes.
Uh... Well, guess that's it.
Sorry to keep you.
Goodbye!
[KYON]
What was that?
Why'd I want to talk to her?
[phone rings]
[KYON] The next morning, I was
wakened from my peaceful slumber
by a call from Haruhi.
She said they'd found
a bon festival.
It was happening tonight
at a park somewhere.
You're late again, Kyon!
Seriously!
What's with you?
Anyway, we're buying yukatas,
and you're coming with us!
[KYON] So, we went
to a clothing outlet,
and Haruhi picked out yukatas
for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then, she marched them straight
into the changing rooms.
And... after making us wait
about an hour or so,
the three of them
finally appeared.
[HARUHI]
What d'ya think?
[gasps]
We look pretty hot, don't we?
Yes, the three of you look
wonderful in them.
Of course we do!
I picked all of 'em out myself,
especially Mikuru's!
Just look at you, you look
so darn cute in that!
I'm like a fashion genius!
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON] Miss Asahina,
please spin around. Spin!
Wow!
This is amazing!
Yeah, this place
looks super fun!
[KYON]
A bon festival, huh?
Yeah... I guess it
figures it'd be so...
...crowded.
[gasps]
[KYON] Whoa, there's that
weird feeling again.
--[HARUHI] Look, Mikuru!
--[KYON gasps]
Over there! They've got goldfish
scooping, just like you wanted!
Come on, I bet you're
gonna catch a ton!
Do you wanna go scoop
some fish, too?
We could have a little contest.
I think I'll pass.
How 'bout you, Nagato?
Wanna get some food?
Huh?
What's up, Nagato?
Don't tell me you're actually
into that stuff.
I got it.
No.
[NAGATO]
That one.
It's yours for 800 yen!
[KYON] I wish she would've
let me buy that for her...
It's the least I could do after
all she's done for us.
[HARUHI]
I caught thirteen!
But I only kept one
'cause I don't have any
place to put 'em all.
Wow, that's an amazing haul!
Go ahead and have one,
but only one!
Okay, thanks.
Huh? Yuki, what's with the mask?
I bought it.
Oh... Okay.
Anyway, let's go shoot
off some fireworks!
It's the perfect way
to end the day!
[KYON] It was summer,
and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I
wanted to forget about it.
But the truth was, I couldn't
ignore it any longer.
[HARUHI] Cool. Tomorrow, we're
gonna go catch some bugs.
Hey, Haruhi, I don't
want to spoil your fun,
but have you finished
your homework yet?
You gotta be kidding.
That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it
in like three days.
Three days?!
You have to get rid
of that junk first,
so you can spend the
rest of your summer
having fun and not
worrying about it!
It's the only way to get the
most out of your vacation!
[KYON groans] Why does
she have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs
weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying
up the stats for us.
Anyway, tomorrow we're
gonna go catch some bugs!
And the prize for whoever
catches the most is gonna be...
Yeah, I know. [gigggles]
Whoever catches the most gets
to be brigade leader for a day!
[KYON]
Ew.
That sounds like a lot of fun!
Are we allowed to catch
just any random bug?
Oh! Um... [laughs]
No, only cicadas! Yeah!
I'm calling it the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest!
[KYON] The next day was
beautiful, sunny, and bright.
In fact, it was the
perfect day for us
to have our SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest.
And even though everyone
caught bugs the best way
they knew how, the winner of
the contest ended up being...
You guessed it, Haruhi.
It's important to
follow the spirit of
catch and release
with these guys.
I mean, if we let
'em go this time,
they might come back and
return the favor some day!
[KYON] What could
a cicada do for me,
even if it did come back?
[HARUHI]
Hurry! Go back to the mountains!
[cicadas chirping]
[KYON]
I sorta feel like Pandora,
when she opened her box.
[MIKURU]
Welcome to our store!
[KYON]
We met the next day,
even though we had no
idea what was going on.
Then, we were forced
to wear frog costumes
and hand balloons out in front
of the local supermarket.
[MIKURU gasps]
Awesome job today, guys!
[KYON] What's with
the special treatment?!
You're the best!
And the manager's super grateful
for all the hard work.
[KYON] Who cares how grateful
he is? What about our pay?
That's it!
Huh?
[HARUHI] I've had my eye on that
little guy for a long time now.
The manager said
we could have it
'cause Mikuru looks
so cute in it!
[KYON]
We worked in the sun,
sweat pouring down
our foreheads...
...for that?!
[HARUHI] We'll keep him in
the club room as a souvenir.
And Mikuru, you can wear him
whenever you want.
Just help yourself!
You have my permission!
Uh...
[sighs]
[KYON] And later that night, my
peace slumber was interrupted...
...by a phone call.
--[phone rings]
--Huh?
[growls]
[MIKURU whimpers]
[gasps]
[MIKURU]
Kyon...
Miss Asahina?
[MIKURU]
Yes... It's me...
[sobbing] Something...
really bad...
I don't know...
W-W-What do I do...
Uh...
--[KOIZUMI] Hello!
--[gasps]
[KOIZUMI]
It's Koizumi.
What are you doing
with Miss Asahina
in the middle of the night?!
[KOIZUMI]
We have a situation over here.
Do you think you could
come meet us right away?
Abso-freaking-lutely.
[MIKURU sobbing]
[KYON]
Miss Asahina! What happened?
What's wrong?
Oh, Kyon... I... I can't...
I can't go back to
the future anymore!
Huh?
I'll explain it the best I can.
We're stuck in a time loop that,
as far as I can tell,
has no end.
[KYON] It's hard to believe
you're actually serious
with you sitting there,
smiling like that.
I mean, come on, do you have any
idea what you just said? Huh?
Of course, I do. Much more
than I want to, believe me.
I was having a little chat
with Miss Asahina earlier.
[KYON] Next time, call me!
And you stay home!
[KOIZUMI] And that was when the
two of us came to the conclusion
that something
seemed a little off
about the current flow of time.
Well, actually, it was Miss
Asahina who discovered it.
And thanks to her,
my suspicions were confirmed.
[KYON]
What suspicions?
[KOIZUMI]
That we're stuck in a time loop.
We're re-living the same period
of time, over and over again.
[KYON]
I know; you already said that.
[KOIZUMI] We're bein' forced
to repeat every day between
August the 17th
through the 31st.
In other words, we're in the
middle of what seems to be
an endless summer vacation.
[KYON] Well, at least it's
summer vacation, right?
[KOIZUMI] It's a never-ending,
endless summer vacation.
In other words, in this world,
the future doesn't
exist anymore.
All time stops at
September the 1st.
Seriously, who's
gonna believe that?
Well, for starters, we were sort
of hoping you would believe it.
What about the closed spaces you
were talking about before?
Could it be that we're trapped
inside one of those things?
Mh-hm. This isn't
the same thing.
A specific section of time
has been torn away.
At exactly midnight on August
the 31st, everything resets.
And then time reverts
straight back to
the morning of August the 17th.
That's the process.
[KYON]
What about our--
Wait, what about the
whole world's memories?
[KOIZUMI]
Their memory is reset.
Everyone's memory starts
over from the beginning.
Perfect, it's another
problem involving time.
Although, I guess I
shouldn't be surprised,
especially if there's
a time traveler around.
Oh, no, Miss Asahina
didn't have anything
to do with what's happening.
Okay then, what's causing it?
Miss Suzumiya is.
[sighs]
Oh, I'm sure she doesn't
even realize it.
But somewhere inside
her subconscious,
there's a desire to have summer
vacation last forever.
What the heck?!
You mean she still
hasn't had enough fun?
That's what I think anyway.
Or it's possible, she feels
there's something else
that needs to happen before
summer vacation can end.
[KYON] Oh, man...
The trouble she gets us into
is always galactic in scale.
Well, what do you want
me to do about it?
If I knew that, we'd have this
problem solved by now.
You seem like you're enjoying
this an awful lot.
What's up with that?
Please don't take that the
wrong way, it's nothing.
However, this explains
the feelings of déjà vu
I've been having.
And the ones you've
been having as well.
And now that I think about it,
those feelings were probably
the residue of our memories
from all the instances
where time was reset.
Are we the only ones?
Or can other people feel
this happening, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
But then again, you and I
are exceptions to the rule.
But what about Haruhi?
Does she even realize what's
been going on around here?
No, I don't think she
knows it's happening.
Besides, it would be very bad
for us if she did know about it.
However, there's someone
who doesn't seem
to be affected by the time loop
or these feelings of déjà vu.
As a matter of fact,
this person remembers
everything that's happened.
Are you gonna tell me
who it is or what?
I think you already
know who it is.
Well, is that true?
It is.
You can remember everything?
I can.
You wouldn't know how many times
we've been repeating the
past two weeks, would you?
This would be 15,527
times so far.
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred twenty-seven?
What do you mean 15,527?
Nagato, what are you saying?
You're being totally
serious, aren't you?
I am.
You've gotta be kidding me!
We've been doing the
exact same things,
that many times,
every single time?
[NAGATO]
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,527 repetitions,
we did not attend
a bon festival the 2,391st
time and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival
but did not go to
a goldfish scooping
booth 437 times.
We've had part-time
jobs 9,052 times
and performed six
different types of jobs.
In addition to handing
out balloons,
we worked as movers--
[KYON]
Yeah... Got it...
[KOIZUMI]
Bye.
[sighs]
[KYON]
Fifteen thousand
five-hundred
twenty-seven times...
That's what she said.
Times two weeks... That's, uh...
about... 595 years!
And she's the only one who
remembers everything we've done.
She's had to repeat those same
things, over and over again.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the
same things that many times?
[KYON] The next night,
we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony
of Nagato's apartment.
And Koizumi brought
the telescope.
[chuckles]
[HARUHI]
I wonder if they're real.
What do you mean?
[HARUHI]
Martians.
[KYON]
I kinda hope they aren't.
[HARUHI] Whenever us humans
get around to landing on Mars,
I'm sure the Martians'll pop out
from wherever they're hiding
and say, "Welcome to Mars!"
or somethin' like that.
Oh... This is boring!
I know! I'm gonna
look for UFOs now!
[KYON] I wish I knew what
else she wants to do.
That's the big question, isn't
it?
If we knew the answer,
we'd be well on our way
to solving this thing.
I have an idea we
can try if you want.
What if someone were to suddenly
grab Miss Suzumiya from behind,
and then whispered, "I love
you," right into her ear?
And who's gonna be doing this?!
Can you think of anyone better
suited to play that role?
I'm supposed to tell her I
l-l-lo-- Aw, forget it.
All right then,
how 'bout if I do it?
[chuckles]
I'm just kidding.
I don't think I could pull
that role off anyway.
Besides, it would just
confuse Miss Suzumiya,
and we wouldn't want that.
[KOIZUMI laughs]
[KYON] So, anyway, the next day,
we went to the batting cages.
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato...
You knew about
this time loop thing
way before Miss Asahina,
didn't you?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
Then how come you didn't
say anything about it?
My function is to observe only.
[gasps]
Understood...
[KYON]
We chugged along,
doing all kinds of
summer vacation things.
More fireworks,
goby fishing tournament,
the test of courage,
movie-watching, beach-going...
Heck. We kept going,
and going, and going!
And the whole time,
all I could think was that
none of it was gonna
be enough for Haruhi.
But what could I do about it?
Nothing.
So, we ended up, like we always
did, at August the 30th.
[HARUHI sighs]
[HARUHI] That's it, we've
done everything on our list.
Hmm... But now I'm wondering
if we really did enough.
Hmm... Oh, well. Yeah,
I guess we did a lot.
Unless there's something
else you guys wanna do?
Okay, then...
We pretty much did everything
we set out to do this summer,
so I guess that's good enough.
[KYON]
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
Well, that's it.
We're done for today!
I set tomorrow aside
just in case,
but I guess you can all
take the day off now.
Kay then, see you guys at
the club room on Monday!
[KYON]
Wait, Haruhi.
Well, that's it.
We're done for today!
I set tomorrow aside
just in case,
but I guess you can
all take the day off now.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
There's that feeling again...
And it's stronger
than all the others.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up re-living
the past two weeks
again and again for a
thousand more times!
[KYON]
But what should I do?
There must've been a clue
in something Haruhi said.
But what was it?
What's she been saying
all this time?
I don't know...
I can't... remember...
[KYON]
It's August the 31st.
I haven't done my homework.
Whatever... It doesn't matter.
There's no point in doing it.
I mean, we're just gonna keep
re-living the last
couple of weeks.
Whatever happens next,
whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me
will have to deal with it.