[KOIZUMI] Lord Suzumiya, we have
report from the scout fleet.
The enemy ships
have been located.
[NAGATO] Enemy fleet at altitude
eight minutes, twenty seconds.
Distance to our location
is 6.3 astronomical units
at 60% light speed.
The enemy's fleet consists of
approximately 15,000 ships.
They're here!
We're gonna annihilate 'em!
All ships to battle stations!
Aye, aye, ma'am.
[KOIZUMI]
All ships to battle stations!
Set all reactors
to combat output.
Set all thrusters to
first stage speeds.
3... 2... 1... Ignition!
[MIKURU]
L-Loading all cannons
with super
gravitational torpedoes!
And um... L-Load the
super proton cannon, too.
Um... All cannons
stand by to fire!
[NAGATO]
Maximum boosters.
Initiate electronic warfare.
ECM, ECCMs are
fully operational.
[HARUHI]
Excellent!
All ships, full speed ahead!
Hey, Haruhi, don't you
think it'd be better
if you pulled your
ships back a little bit?
Your fleet shouldn't
be so far in front of us.
[HARUHI]
What are you talking about?!
I wanna shoot beams and
missiles at the enemy, too!
[KYON] Look, when you're
playing shogi or chess,
the king isn't the one who
charges into enemy territory.
Oh, yeah... Good thinking.
Okay, Kyon. You guys
take care of it.
Go find the enemy leader,
and give him a good
pummeling with your cannons!
And make sure you win!
I want you to take those fools
from the Computer Club,
and beat the living daylights
out of those geek boys!
[KYON] Wouldn't it better if we
just raised the white flag now?
Well, I guess that's not
gonna be an option today.
[electronic gunfire]
[KYON] It is autumn now.
And the arts festival ended
several days ago
without incident.
Peace and quiet had
returned to the campus.
You could say, it was just
another ordinary day.
Then again, I shouldn't be so
quick to label an afternoon
spent at the SOS Brigade
headquarters as "ordinary."
I mean, every day,
I hang out with
an alien, a time traveler,
and an ESPer.
And I'm still as sane
and objective as ever.
[KYON]
Hmm...
I wonder if that makes
me special or something.
I'm sure Lacan's dying
to have a word with me.
[KOIZUMI]
You seem worried.
Is something wrong?
[KYON]
Nope.
[KYON] I was just thinking
about how awesome I am
for being able to cope
with this absurd situation.
And if you ask me, I think
I'm due for a little praise.
[KOIZUMI]
You're right.
Well? Would you like me to give
you some words of praise then?
[KYON] You praising me
won't make me any happier.
All it'll do is make me think
you've got something
up your sleeve.
[KOIZUMI laughs]
True enough.
[MIKURU]
I'm sorry this took so long.
I bought this stem
tea called karigane.
It's the first time
I've ever made it,
so I hope I brewed it well!
[KYON]
Nonsense.
If the divine hands of
Miss Asahina touched it,
even tap water would
taste better than
melted snow from the Alps!
[MIKURU giggles]
I hope you like the flavor!
By the way, where's
Miss Suzumiya?
She's got cleanup duty.
[KYON] Sure is peaceful when
she's not around, isn't it?
[KYON sighs]
[knocking]
[MIKURU]
Yes! I'm coming!
[door clicks]
[MIKURU gasps]
It's the president of
the Computer Club.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT] Hm?
Isn't your leader here today?
You guys want something?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT chuckles]
First, I want you to take this.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT] You'll find
some game software on that disc.
Yeah, it's an original game
that we designed and developed.
We had it on display
at the arts festival.
Maybe you saw it?
I don't remember.
[KYON] The only memory I want
to retain from the arts festival
is the image of Miss Asahina
wearing that maid outfit!
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Really?
Perhaps we were exhibiting
it in the wrong place?
[KYON]
So what did you guys want?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT gasps]
That's right!
We've come here to challenge
you and your brigade thing.
[KYON]
Huh?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
A duel!
We fight a duel using our game!
Really, a duel!
We wanna duel against you guys!
[KYON]
I beg you...
Please stop repeating the
word "duel" over and over!
If Haruhi's ultra-sharp
ears could hear you,
you'd be as godd as--
[HARUHI yells]
[GROUP]
Chief!
So, you want a duel?
Who are you guys anyway?
A-ha, I bet you creeps are
some kinda secret syndicate
trying to muscle my
SOS Brigade outta the way.
I won't let that happen!
Annihilating evil and
shining light upon darkness
is the sworn duty
of a hero of justice!
[KYON]
Haruhi? You should listen to
what people have to
say before you kick them.
[HARUHI] Kyon, a duel is a
duel from the very moment
the word is mentioned!
Anything the loser says
after that is just an excuse.
Huh?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT groans]
[HARUHI]
It's you guys?
Why are the Computer Club
geeks pickin' a fight with us?
[KYON] That's exactly what they
were about to explain to us
before you took 'em out.
[HARUHI]
Oh? They were, huh?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Ugh, rotten SOS Brigade.
Whatever!
We, the members of
the Computer Club,
hereby challenge the
SOS Brigade to a duel!
[HARUHI]
A duel, huh?
--[HARUHI growls]
--[COMPUTER PRESIDENT grunts]
[GROUP]
Chief!
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT whimpers]
[KYON] Come on, guys. It's time
to move the story along.
Well? What's this all about?
We made a game, and we
wanna fight you guys in it.
And if we win, you have
to return "it" to us.
[HARUHI]
What do you mean? Return what?
If you're not using it,
give back our computer!
But, I use this
thing all the time!
A coupla days ago,
we cut our movie on it.
[KYON]
Actually, I did that.
[HARUHI] And we made
our homepage with it.
[KYON]
Yep, did that, too.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
What are you talking about?!
You barely even
update your homepage!
[KYON] Ah-hah, so he's the guy
who's always visiting our site.
That explains the camel cricket.
Wait a second, when I
went over there,
and I said I wanted it,
you said you'd give it to me!
You remember it, too.
Don't you, Kyon?
You sure about that?
The deal is off!
And besides,
you bullied me into it!
In fact, I'm even willing to
forget the mental trauma
you inflicted upon me when
you abducted my computer.
Yes, I want to forget it.
We should both forget it.
Anyway, whatever! We wanna
fight you, you got it?!
Sure, you got it.
If you wanna fight us so bad,
then we accept your challenge!
Now then, what do you
guys give us if we win?
Well, let's see...
How about four
brand new laptops?
That's one laptop
for each member.
[HARUHI]
Are you serious?!
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Oh, yes.
[HARUHI]
Really?
I'm not gonna let you call it
off if you change your mind.
You understand?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Don't worry. You have my word.
You're pretty confident,
aren't you? All right.
Now that I think about it,
you guys don't have
any girls in your club.
If you guys beat us,
we'll give her to you.
How 'bout that?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Huh?!
I'm sure you guys can
find a good use for Yuki!
Since you're putting up four
computers against the one
we have, Yuki helps to
even out the stakes!
--Yeah! Well, I-I--
--[KYON] No.
There's a big
difference between
the specs of four
laptops and Nagato.
But you wouldn't know that.
Really? Then do you
want Mikuru instead?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT gasps]
[KYON]
Why don't you be the prize?
If you're gonna bet anything,
how 'bout you go ahead
and bet your own body?
Stop being so selfish for once.
What are you talking about?!
Are you forgetting
that I'm the divine
and sacred figurehead
of the SOS Brigade?!
I'm your leader, dummy!
I will never give
up this position
except to the person I
feel is the chosen one.
[KYON] You mean
you're gonna stay here
even after you graduate?!
What's it gonna be?
Who do you prefer?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Well-- I-- Uh...
I see, so that's
how it's gonna be.
If you insist, you can have me.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
No! No! Absolutely no. No way.
[HARUHI]
Hm?
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
The game is an online
space battle simulator.
Five players versus five.
The battle will begin at 4:00,
one week from today.
Until then, you should
brush up on your skills.
We'll be disappointed
if you're too weak.
[KYON] He's acting
like he's already won.
How generous of you to give
us our prizes in advance!
Mm-hmm!
After all, each brigade member
should have their own computer!
[KYON] And she's acting
the exact same way.
[KYON]
About this duel coming up,
let's just try not
to cheat, okay?
[KOIZUMI]
Cheat? Us?
Yeah, this time around,
all alien, futuristic, and ESPer
methods of cheating are
100% completely
off-limits. You got that?
We will fight fairly and
accept the outcome,
whatever that may be.
That is the best way.
Then you won't mind if we
just happen to lose the game.
That's right. The only
thing we're gonna lose
is that computer
we stole from them.
And I guess that's
not such a big deal.
[KYON]
Although, if that does happen,
I'm gonna need to relocate
the Asahina gallery.
Oh, I'm not talkin'
about the computer.
Miss Suzumiya doesn't like
to lose at anything, ever.
Remember?
[KOIZUMI] Whenever she feels
like she's going to lose,
she creates closed space.
And then, she lets those
you-know-what's loose.
You'll be okay with that?
I don't really care.
Besides, it's about damn time
that girl learned her lesson.
--KOIZUMI chuckles]
--[KYON] Hm?
What's up?
You're creeping me out.
No, sorry. I just got
a bit jealous, is all.
I admit, I'm a little envious
of the invisible trust
that exists between Miss
Suzumiya and yourself.
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about.
Let's say we lose the game
against the Computer
Club next week,
and based on what you've
already seen with your own eyes,
you're choosing to
believe that Miss Suzumiya
won't create a closed
space this time.
Well? That's because
you trust her.
Then, there's Miss Suzumiya.
She believes you're the one
who's goin' to lead
our team to victory.
So, she trusts you.
She's so confident
she's going to win
that she'd risk losing her
own members in the wager.
That, is trust.
[KOIZUMI] Although she'd never
come right out and say it,
the truth of the matter is
that between the two of you,
there is the most ideal
bond of trust I've ever seen.
[electronic gunfire]
[KOIZUMI] "The Day of
Sagittarius Part Three," huh?
So there was a part one and
part two before this version?
[HARUHI]
Lame.
Sounds like they were going
for something cool sounding.
Doesn't make any sense, though.
[KYON]
What're you talking about?
Is the "SOS Brigade" any better?
Well, at least the game
looks simple enough to play.
Each of the five players
is given a fleet of
15,000 space ships,
which they're able to command
from their own computer.
You win the game by destorying
all the enemy ships
or by blowing up the
enemy leader's flagship.
What's with this bright spot?
[KOIZUMI]
That's your line of sight.
You can see enemy and obstacles
only when they're
inside that bubble.
In order to play,
you'll have to send out
scout ships from your fleet
to increase your
field of vision.
Basically, in order
to win this thing,
it looks like you need to find
out where your enemy is,
and take 'em out
as fast as you can.
[MIKURU] So you can't see
the enemy in the beginning?
Um, Kyon? I, uh... I'm not
really good at stuff like this.
I don't think I
understand it at all.
Hey, don't worry.
Just take your time,
get used to the controls,
and try and have
some fun with it.
This is not supposed to be fun!
We're gonna crush the
Computer Club so hard,
they won't be able to stand up!
Now let's get some
training happening!
Naturally, I'll be
commanding this outfit.
Now hop to it! Battle positions!
[KYON] At least we've
got Nagato on our side.
I take it back. We're dead!
[HARUHI]
All ships, attack!
[explosions]
[GROUP]
Aww!
[HARUHI]
All ships, attack!
[explosions]
[GROUP]
Aww!
[HARUHI]
All ships, attack!
[explosions]
[GROUP]
Aww!
[HARUHI]
All ships, attack!
--[explosions]
--[GROUP] Aww!
[HARUHI growls]
We got beat again!
Killing in this rotten
game's irritating me!
It's because you
keep rushing in!
You don't just charge into
battle in the beginning.
Geez! This thing is such a drag!
I'd much rather play something
easier to understand.
[KYON groans]
Is it just me or are you
having fun over there?
I meant what I said before,
There's absolutely no
cheating this time, okay?
[HARUHI] Today, the skies are
clear and the waves are high.
This battle will decide
the destiny of the empire!
And believe me, this is
just the beginning.
We'll vaporize anything
that gets in our way.
The SOS Brigade will
make its name known
to the ends of the universe!
One day, I'll talk to the
Board of Education about
creating branches of the SOS
Brigade in every public school!
Obviously, we're going to win,
but I still won't
allow any slacking!
Now, pulverize 'em!
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] Whatever gives her
that confidence, I want it.
Even if it's only
two miligrams, I want it.
Oh, really?
Do you want me to
pump some into you?
[HARUHI giggles]
There! Bet that did the trick!
What good does it
do to stare at me
and make me uncomfortable?
[HARUHI] I charged my glare
with a bunch of energy
and sent it to you!
You probably felt something
like your body getting warmer.
Maybe you're starting to sweat!
You feel it, don't you?
You feel it?
[KYON] No, I felt like
my life was in danger.
Looks like the
game's about to begin.
[countdown beeping]
[beep]
All ships, ahead!
[KYON]
Well, the game's begun.
And as luck would have it,
we've just run
across an enemy fleet.
Thanks to Nagato,
we 've somehow managed to figure
out the enemy's movements.
She scouts and fights
the enemy simultaneously.
Talk about bravery.
[MIKURU screaming]
[KYON]
Miss Asahina, the gamig novice,
and Haruhi, the charging idiot,
are completely useless.
It's five against three, and
we're the ones outnumbered.
The enemy's usin' a "V"
formation to try to lure us
into their firing range.
I think we should counter
with a defensive strategy.
Sounds like a great plan.
But what would Haruhi say
about this strategy of yours?
--[explosion]
--[KYON groans]
What the--?!
[KYON] We're being attacked
by another enemy fleet?
Where'd these guys come from?!
They're goin'
after my fleet, too!
How did they figure
out where we were?
What're you doing?! Hurry up
and start retaliating!
I didn't need you
to tell me that.
Starboard, 90 degrees.
Open all cannons.
[KOIZUMI] It sounds like
someone's getting serious
about this game.
[KYON]
Enemy fleet in range!
Beam cannons, open fire!
Wait, hang on!
Damn, they got away.
Same over here. They
unloaded on us for a bit,
then they vanished
into thin air.
The old hit-and-run tactic, huh?
[KOIZUMI]
Whoa! They're back. Other side.
[KYON]
They're just picking us off.
[HARUHI]
What are you doing, slow poke?!
They're getting away!
[KYON] I know! But I can't
do anything to stop them!
Those jerks are hitting
us from both sides!
[HARUHI]
It's time to launch the ---dams.
[KYON]
Here I go! Wait!
[whimpering]
Um...
Can someone please tell
me where I am right now?
[HARUHI]
Ugh! I can't take this anymore!
Attention, fleets!
Full speed ahead!
I'm gonna find the enemy leader
and pummel him to bits!
[KYON]
What're you doing? Pull back!
[KOIZUMI]
He's right; leave this to us!
[HARUHI]
Out of my way!
The leaders are gonna
duke this out, one on one!
[KYON] Fall back! We don't
even know where he is!
[HARUHI] Then leave it
to me! I'll find him!
[KYON]
I'm telling you, fall back!
[KOIZUMI] Let's calm down.
The enemy's shooting at us.
[MIKURU] Hey, guys!
Where did everyone go?
[HARUHI]
Move!
[KYON]
I can't! I'm stuck here!
We're gonna lose
this thing. Huh?
[KYON gasps]
What the...?!
[KOIZUMI]
Wow, she split up her fleet.
You can do that?
I remember reading about it
in the back of the manual.
Apparently, you can split your
fleet up into 20 squadrons
and control them separately.
The thing is, it isn't
humanly possible to control
so many squadrons
at the same time.
So, nobody was doing it.
[KYON]
Isn't humanly possible, huh?
[MIKURU]
Um... Uh...
Aren't you afraid
you'll break the keyboard
hitting it that hard?
[HARUHI] Anyone accepting
defeat will be punished
by running ten laps
around the school!
Naked!
And you'll have to yell,
"Green martians
are chasing me!" for
the whole ten laps!
Uh... You know... Hm?
[KYON]
Um, Miss Nagato? Yeah, hi.
What exactly are
you doing right now?
Hey, Nagato.
[NAGATO]
What?
I thought I told you before
that we weren't
gonna cheat this time.
[NAGATO]
I am not.
Currently, I am not engaged
in manipulating special data.
I am adhering to
the rules of the game.
Uh-- You're serious?
[NAGATO]
I am serious.
The Computer Club is
the one that is cheating.
They are? Then, what
are they doing?
[NAGATO] They've deactivated
their scouting mode.
Since the beginning of the game,
everything on the map,
including our positions,
has been visible.
It's amazing! I understood
what you just said.
They've got it fixed so that we
can't see where they're hiding,
but they can see where we are.
It's no wonder
they're killing us.
Yes.
Since we started playing,
we never had any
option except losing.
I want to change that.
[KYON sighs]
Okay, they've been cheating,
I understand that.
However, if we start using
magic to cheat back at them,
at the end of the day,
we're no better than they are!
You get where I'm coming from?
In fact, we'd be
worse than them.
I repeat, I am not
disobeying your orders.
I would like to modify
the program in a matter
that is consistent with the
current levels of earth
technology. ensuring equal
playing conditions.
May I?
[KYON gasps]
Are you doing this
because you want to win?
[KYON]
Uh...
[chuckles]
Okay! Let's do it then!
Done.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Nice! Very Nice!
I was a little worried there
when they fired up
the squadron mode,
but we've still got
the advantage.
We see them,
but they can't see us.
Time to wrap this up.
Destroy them!
Annihilate the SOS Brigade!
Wha...?!
[MEMBER A] Chief! Scouting
mode has been activated!
[MEMBER B] They're
attacking our blind spot!
[MEMBER C] We can't
figure out their movements!
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
What're you idiots doing?!
Deactivate scouting mode!
Turn it off!
[MEMBER A] We can't
change it! It's denying access!
We're locked out!
That's... Impossible!
I gotcha!
Fire, fire, fire!
Say good night!
[HARUHI]
Damn you, Kyon!
That's my enemy!
We've managed to destroy
two of the enemy's fleets.
And the otherse are
lookin' a bit confused.
Thanks to Miss Nagato's
squadrons, it looks like the
tides of war have finally
turned in our favor.
[KYON] Yeah, but the enemy
leader's still out there.
So how're we gonna take him out?
[NAGATO]
No problem.
I'll force him your way.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT yelps]
Dammit!
Wow, he's driving his
fleet right into our sights!
Just like a mouse
caught in a trap.
Um... Am I supposed
to shoot this thing?
I don't get what just happened,
but great job, guys!
All ships, open fire!
Go out there and
burn the enemy leader
with all the fires of hell!
He's getting away!
This can't be happening!
Glory to the Computer Club!
[HARUHI giggles]
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
I lost... We were beaten...
I'll apologize now.
I admit it, I'm sorry.
But I can't believe... I--
I just can't believe the program
was rewritten during gameplay!
That's impossible!
[HARUHI]
What are you mumbling about?
Whatever. You do remember
your promise, right?
These laptops belong
to the SOS Brigade now,
and I won't let
you back out of it.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Hey... Um...
[KYON]
Hm?
Tell me, I wanna
know who did it.
Wheover cracked that program has
to be some kinda super hacker.
Nevermind, I think
I know who it was.
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Uh...
If you ever have free time,
I was wondering
if you'd consider
participating in Computer
Club activities. Please?
[KYON] Great, he's trying
to recruit Yuki.
Whoa! Hang on! You can't just
rent Yuki without my permission!
Got it!?
She's the silent character in
the SOS Brigade line-up!
And besides, I saw
her first, so there!
Hang on.
[KYON] I think that even
someone like Nagato
has to have other interests.
Now, I can't be sure,
but it looked to me like
she was having fun,
pounding away on that keyboard.
Besides, I'll bet
she gets tired of
observing Haruhi all
the time. I know I would.
I mean, even a
humanoid interface
designed for contact
with organic life forms
needs a break
every now and then.
Just do what you want, okay?
If you feel like
going next door,
and playing around
on their computers,
it's totally cool.
Oh.
Perhaps I will.
--[HARUHI gasps]
--Seriously?!
Oh, thank you!
There you go.
I guess it's okay if
Yuki's fine with it.
Oh, by the way...
[COMPUTER PRESIDENT]
Eh?
The Computer Club lost the game!
And as the losers,
you have to do whatever
the winners tell you to do!
What?!
[HARUHI]
All you need to do is
swear your absolute
loyalty to me.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll treat you nice.
[sighs]
[HARUHI]
And if you guys work real hard,
I just might let you become
a member of the brigade!
Koizumi! Draw up a
contract for him to sign!
[KOIZUMI]
As you wish, Your Highness.