[GIRL A] Next up is the
inter-club relay race.
[START]
On your mark...
Get set...
[cheering]
[MIKURU whimpering]
[KYON]
Here I go!
Here.
[gasps]
[gunshots]
[HARUHI]
Darn it.
I wanted to come from last place
and pass everyone at the end!
But thanks to Yuki,
we blew 'em away,
and left 'em
chokin' on our dust!
It was a fantastic
effort though.
I just hope the track team
doesn't lost their confidence
because of our excellence.
Come on, guys,
this isn't funny at all.
Everybody's gonna
think we're weirder now,
than they ever did before.
[KYON] Although, it's a little
late to be worrying about that.
[KYON] And yes, the outfits and
the headbands with odd phrases
were all Haruhi's idea, but I
bet you knew that already.
Why are we doing this again?
Okay, that's it.
Can I change out
of this thing now?
You and Miss Suzumiya's
band of freaks
are still the weirdest
cats in school.
It's epic stuff, my brother.
Keep up the good work, you hear?
Cut it out.
I'm doing everything I can to be
as low-profile around
here as possible.
Running in that outfit was
definitely low-profile, sir.
Well, it wasn't easy,
let me tell you.
Yeah, I think you're
sorta missing the point.
I bet they're gonna
stick a picture of you
wearing that in the yearbook.
Can't wait to see that.
Gimme a break already.
[TANIGUCHI whistles]
Huh?
Who's that?
Ew!
Gross.
[TANIGUCHI] Did you see
the one with the ponytail?
She's such a cutie pie!
[KYON] Our neverending, endless
summer vacation had ended.
And here we were, second term,
and having an athletic festival.
Of course, Haruhi wasn't
gonna sit still
on a beautiful day like today.
Just look at the poor
souls left in her wake.
[KYON]
Yeah... That's Haruhi.
She sure loves her
festivals, doesn't she?
[KYON] Our bizarre day of
athletic festivities was over.
It was the beginning
of a new month,
and our school arts festival
was right around the corner.
And, as you can see, everyone
was busy getting ready for it.
[KYON] By the way,
if you were wondering
what me and Haruhi's
class were doing,
check out the board.
Yep, we wussed out, and
decided that our class project
was gonna be some
kind of survey.
Ever since Ryoko Asakura "left"
back in the spring term,
there wasn't anyone crazy enough
to take over the leadership
duties of our class.
We're going, Kyon.
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] So, with a level of
disinterest bordering on apathy,
I find myself once again
trudging over to the club room.
Why? Well, I'll tell you why.
It's all because the girl who's
marching along beside me
said the following:
I can't believe our project
is gonna be a survey.
That's gotta be the dumbest
idea I've ever heard!
Why did they have to go and
pick the least fun thing to do?
Well, maybe you should've
said something about it
when you had the chance.
Didn't you see the class?
And that look on
Mr. Okabe's face?
It was like someone had died.
Oh, whatever.
It wasn't like I was
gonna participate
in anything the class
was doing anyway.
[KYON]
Hmm.
Although, I think I remember
you having something to do
with our class winning the
track and field championships.
And, if I'm not mistaken,
weren't you the one
who entered every event
and won all of them?
That was you, wasn't it?
Or was that someone else?
[HARUHI] This and that
are two different things.
I'm talking about the
school arts festival.
It's like the most important,
super event we get a year!
Oh, it is, is it?
Absolutely!
And this year, we're gonna
do something so cool,
it's gonna blow everyone's mind!
[KYON] The look on Haruhi's
face when she said that,
full of confidence
and shining brightly,
it must've been what
Hannibal looked like
as he crossed the Alps
during the Second Punic War!
It's the school arts festival!
So get with the program,
and act more excited about it!
[KYON chuckles]
[HARUHI] This is the
only chance we'll get
to experience this
as tenth graders!
I know, I got it.
But I just don't see
the point in getting
all riled up about it.
But if you don't get
all riled up about it,
then there's no
point in doing it!
All the school festivals I've
ever been to were like that.
[KYON]
Did you guys go all out
at your old junior
high or something?
[HARUHI]
Not even.
They were all pretty lame.
That's why I want all my high
school festivals to be exciting!
[KYON] Then, what'll it take to
make this one exciting for you?
[KYON] And please, explain it
so I can understand.
Oh, all right.
I'll tell you about it when
we get to the club room.
[KYON gasps]
The scent of lavender!
Oh! Hello, there!
[KYON]
I thought flowers were blooming.
I'll go prepare some tea, okay?
[KYON]
Oh, don't trouble yourself.
Stop it, you look
like a dirty old man!
Hey, Mikuru, where's Koizumi?
[MIKURU]
He hasn't come by yet.
I think he's running late.
[water pouring]
[HARUHI] Mikuru,
what's holding up the tea?
[MIKURU]
I-I'm bringing it now!
Mikuru.
[MIKURU]
Yes?
Don't you remember all that
stuff we talked about before?
[MIKURU]
Huh? What do you mean?
I mean, whenever you serve tea,
you have to try to make
sure you trip and stumble
at least a third of the time!
You know, you're not acting
like a klutsy maid at all.
[MIKURU]
Huh? Oh. S-Sorry!
[KYON]
What's up with her?
Does she think all maids have
to be clumsy or something?
Don't worry.
Today's your lucky day.
You get to go and
practice on Kyon!
Your goal is to get the cup to
land upside-down on his head!
Really?
Miss Asahina,
Haruhi's the only person
who's gonna think a
joke like that is funny.
--You should know that by now.
--[MIKURU whimpers]
[HARUHI]
Hey, dummy.
I never joke about
stuff like that.
I am always super serious!
[KYON] If that's the case,
then we're in big trouble!
All right, Mikuru,
I'll demonstrate the
proper technique,
and then it's your turn.
But I-- Huh?
[KYON gasps]
Hey!
Hold it!
Hey, you! Stop interfering!
Are you crazy?
I'm not gonna just sit
here and do nothing
while you pour boiling
water on my head!
[HARUHI]
Hmph!
[MIKURU chuckles]
[MIKURU]
Here you are.
[KYON]
Oh, Nagato.
If she made Taniguchi a cup,
he'd cherish it for three days!
[door opens]
I'm sorry, everyone.
Homeroom ran a
little late today.
I hope our meeting
wasn't delayed too long
because of my tardiness.
Wait, what meeting?
What's he talking about?
[KYON]
Yeah, I forgot to tell you,
but I let everyone else
know about it at lunch today.
I guess I just figured
I'd tell you whenever.
How come you have
the time to go to
their classrooms
and tell them?!
I sit right in front
of you all day long.
Telling me couldn't
be any easier!
Yeah, like it even matters.
The problem isn't so much
when you found out about it,
it's what you're
going to do about it!
[KYON] Was that
supposed to be profound?
The SOS Brigade's
gotta start thinking now
about what we're gonna do next!
[KYON] Are we talking
about now-now or later?
And by "we," did you
mean we as in us?
Or "we" as in you?
Everyone here is
gonna participate.
This is an SOS Brigade
event, after all.
And by that, you mean...
We were just talking about it!
The school arts festival, what
else is going on around here?!
Right, well that's something
the whole school's involved in.
And if you're so
hot and bothered
about being the main attraction,
you should've signed up
to be on the festival staff.
[KYON] They probably could
use all the help they can get.
[HARUHI]
That's a total waste of time!
We have to do something that's
up to SOS Brigade standards.
I worked hard to
build this brigade
into the coolest thing
the school's ever seen.
Everyone knows about us!
We've got a
reputation to uphold!
[KYON] It's easy for
you 'cause all you do
is come up with crazy schemes.
Miss Asahina and I have
to suffer through them
Koizumi just sits there,
smiling like a weirdo.
And Nagato never helps
with the brainstorming.
I'm the normal one here.
She should consider
that for a change.
[HARUHI]
We have to do something
that lives up to
their expectations.
[KYON] Now what exactly
does anyone expect
from the SOS Brigade?
I know, let's take a
survey and find out!
Hey, Mikuru, what's
your class gonna do?
[MIKURU]
My class?
Um...
A yakisoba cafe.
I bet that means you're
gonna be a waitress, huh?
How did you know about that?
Everyone in my class
said I'd be perfect for it.
[HARUHI]
Hmm...
[chuckles]
[HARUHI]
What about you, Koizumi?
Well, my class decided
it would be fun
if we put on a play.
But we're debating
whether to do a classic
or something original.
[KYON] Now they sound like
a lively bunch of people.
[KYON]
And pretty annoying.
[HARUHI]
Ohh...
And Yuki?
Fortune-telling.
Really?
Yes.
[KYON] Nagato telling fortunes?
Or telling futures?
Oh! I got a great idea!
How 'bout this?
Let's mix everything
together and
do a survey-cafe-
fortune-telling-theater!
Stop being a dork and let's get
this meeting started already!
[KYON growls]
Not sure what you
want us to look at.
There's nothing
written on it yet.
Just hold your horses.
Hey, Mikuru. Since you're
the secretary,
make sure you write
everything down.
[MIKURU]
Uh... Okay.
[KYON] I didn't know Miss
Asahina was our secretary.
I doubt anyone knows
'cause it's something
Haruhi just came up with.
We, the SOS Brigade,
are gonna show a movie
at this year's festival!
[KYON]
Huh?
[KYON] I have absolutely
no idea what goes on
inside that head of hers.
And I don't wanna know.
This is typical Haruhi.
However...
How in the heck
is this a meeting?
It's like you're on a soapbox
giving a political speech.
This is normal for us.
[KYON]
Ugh! Too close!
It looks like Miss
Suzumiya decided on
what we were gonna do
right from the beginning,
and negotiations are
out of the question.
But I wonder why she
decided on a movie.
Maybe she saw a really
bad flick on TV last night.
And if the movie was
especially horrible,
it could have put her in a
lousy mood or something.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[HARUHI]
You know,
there's something I
always wondered about.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[KYON] I wonder what's
inside your head.
How come on TV shows,
when they get to the last
episode, someone dies?
That always feels
really fake to me.
I mean, their deaths
are so convenient.
It's weird.
I guess that's why I can't stand
shows or movies or anything
where a character
dies at the end.
I would never make a
movie that ended like that.
[HARUHI]
Mm-hmm.
That's what I mean!
Now do you get it?
What do you mean,
"That's what I mean"?
All you said was that we're
gonna be showing a movie.
But where's this
movie coming from?
Oh, Kyon, you're not
very smart, are you?
We are gonna make our own movie.
And then, we're gonna show
it at the school arts festival!
And the credits are gonna read:
"Presented by the SOS Brigade."
When exactly did we
become the Movie Club?
What are you talking about?
We're still the SOS Brigade.
Nobody said we turned
into the Movie Club.
[KOIZUMI] I think I
understand what's going on.
[GROUP]
Huh?
She's saying we're going
to shoot our own movie,
and then screen it
during the arts festival.
That's the plan, isn't it?
That is the plan!
But um... why did you
decide to shoot a movie?
If you really wanna know,
I was having trouble
falling asleep last night.
I turned on the TV and
this crappy movie was on.
[KYON]
I knew it!
It had to be the worst movie
I've ever seen in my whole life!
It was so bad, for a sec there,
I was thinking about
crank-calling the director!
--[MIKURU yelps]
--And that's when it hit me!
If that's the best they can do,
I can definitely
make a better movie!
Uh-huh...
So I figured, what the
heck, let's go for it!
[whimpers]
If you wanna be a
director or a producer,
that's fine with me.
Good for you, godspeed,
and so on and so forth.
But, some of us might
have other things
we'd like to do, you know?
What do you mean?
What would you do if we said
we didn't feel like doing this?
I mean, think about it.
You can't make a movie
with just a director.
Don't worry about that!
I'm almost done with the script!
Yeah... I don't
think you understood
what I was talking about there.
Oh, come on, don't sweat
the small stuff.
Just follow my lead like always,
and everything will be fine!
You don't have to worry
about anything at all!
[KYON]
I'm worried.
Just leave everything to me!
I'm gonna plan
the whole thing out!
[KYON]
Now I'm really worried.
I said we're doing it,
and that's that.
Stop being so annoying.
Our goal is to be voted the
#1 event of the festival!
Maybe then, those jerks
in the student council
will recognize the SOS
Brigade as a legitimate club!
No, we're gonna
make 'em recognize us.
And to do that, we're gonna need
to get the public on our side.
And how are we gonna
pay for all this?
We'll just dip into our funds.
What funds?
[HARUHI] We've got
the literary club's money.
[KYON] But that's their
money for their projects.
You can't just
decide to take it.
Yuki, is it okay if
I have your money?
Yes.
[HARUHI]
Listen up, people!
Whatever your classes are doing,
this is more important!
If anyone thinks different,
we'll talk about it
after the festival.
The director's will is supreme!
Got it?!
[KYON] First, she's the brigade
leader. Now, she's a director.
What does she wanna be next?
Please, please don't say god.
[HARUHI]
Okay. We're done for today!
Since I'm producing this thing,
I've got a lot to think about!
We'll go over all
the details tomorrow.
[MIKURU sighs]
This isn't such a bad thing.
If you want to know the truth,
I'm actually quite
relieved this is happening.
It's not like we have to catch a
space monster for a slide show.
Or shoot down a UFO and
make an exhibit out of it.
Besides, I'm a
little curious to see
what kind of movie Miss
Suzumiya wants to shoot.
This should make for
an interesting festival,
very interesting indeed.
D-Did you want something?
[KYON] Nothing... Just
wondering what kind of costume
Haruhi was gonna
bring in next, that's it.
Shooting a movie... Uh-oh.
[KYON]
A movie, huh?
To be honest, I was kind
of interested in the idea.
Not as much as Koizumi though.
I guess, at the very least,
I should try to be
more psyched about it.
[KYON] After all, I doubt
anyone's expecting much.
[KYON gasps]
I take back everything I said.
I shouldn't have been psyched.
Because the next day,
after school,
I became very, very sad.
So, what exactly am I
supposed to do on this thing?
[HARUHI]
Take a look; it's on the board.
Am I really supposed
to be the heroine?
Because if it's possible,
I'd like to play a part
that's less prominent...
[HARUHI] No way! You're gonna
play the flashiest role ever!
Besides, you're kinda
the brigade's mascot.
Oh! And you might wanna start
practicing your autograph!
When we have the premiere,
I bet you're gonna get
swarmed by a ton of fans!
[KYON] Where are you
gonna hold a premiere?
But, I've never acted
in anything before.
Don't worry about a thing!
I'm an awesome director!
[HARUHI giggles]
I am a little concerned about
Yuki and Koizumi though.
They know this
project takes priority,
but they're still in class.
I have to give them a
warning for showing up late.
[KYON] It's a little odd
that me and Miss Asahina
were here on time
and ready to go though.
Hm?
Miss Asahina, is it
okay that you're here
and not at your class meeting?
[MIKURU]
Mm-hmm.
Since I'm just going
to be a waitress,
all I have to do is get
fitted for my costume.
I'm kind of looking
forward to it.
Actually, I can't wait!
[KYON] Miss Asahina's
blushing smile proved
that she'd gotten
used to cosplaying.
Well, at least now, she'll get
to wear the proper costume
for the proper occasion.
More than she does for
the SOS Brigade, anyway.
If you really wanna
be a waitress,
I can totally make that happen!
I've got a buncha costumes
I can bring in for you!
Just let me know, okay?
By the way, Kyon, what's the
one thing every movie
has to have before
you start shooting?
[KYON]
Hmm...
I guess it would
be an original idea
and the passion to tell
a compelling story.
No, you need a camera.
How're we gonna shoot a
movie without a camera?
I wasn't looking for one
of your abstract answers.
[KYON] That's fine, but I
didn't wanna give you an answer
that sounded
too practical, either.
Whatever...
Here's what we're doing next:
Our mission is to go find
ourselves a video camera!
[thud]
[MIKURU whimpering]
M-Miss Suzumiya...
There's something I have to do,
so c-could I go
back to my class?
Shut up and sit down.
[MIKURU whimpers]
There's no need to worry!
[KYON]
I've yet to find an occasion
when you told us not to worry,
and we really didn't
have to worry.
[HARUHI] Look, it's not like
I'm gonna use your body
to pay for that stuff we need.
I just need your
help today, that's all.
[MIKURU whimpering]
You're gonna tell us
what you need her for.
If you don't, Miss Asahina and I
refuse to get outta
these chairs to help.
We have to go look for sponsors!
They'll take us more seriously
if we have the
lead actress there.
And you're gonna come, too.
I need some help carrying stuff.
[KYON]
It's supposed to be fall now,
but the temperature
hasn't cooled off.
I guess the planet has finally
gone completely insane,
'cause it forgot to switch the
season in Japan over to fall.
[KYON] After we finished
walking down the hill,
we hopped on the local line and
took it for about three stops.
Our destination wasn't too far
from that place with
the cherry trees,
where Miss Asahina and I
had that talk a while ago.
[train screeches]
We're here!
We are indeed.
[KYON]
I guess this is the store
she's planning on getting
all our equipment from.
I wonder how she's
gonna do it though.
You guys wait here.
I'm gonna go inside
and talk to the guy.
Here! Hang onto this!
Okay.
[KYON]
I swear,
if Haruhi does anything
even remotely suspicious,
I'm gonna grab Miss
Asahina and split.
[KYON] I should probably warn
that relatively pleasant looking
man that nodding his head
at whatever Haruhi's saying
is a very, very bad idea.
I wonder what she's doing.
Dunno.
She's probably asking about
one of the high-end
digital cameras he's sells.
And knowing how she operates,
I bet she's tryin' to get
it for nothing, too.
[KYON]
She's definitely someone
who would try to do
something like that.
She's such a pain.
Haruhi thinks her ideals
and opinions are absolute.
And sometimes, she even
thinks other people
share her warped
views about things.
Well, actually, that pretty
much happens all the time,
so I guess you could
say she just doesn't get it.
If you wanna go faster
than the speed of light,
make sure Haruhi's
on your space ship.
She'd just ignore the
laws of relativity for you.
Look! I think they finished.
[HARUHI giggling]
[HARUHI]
Ta-da!
Our first mission was a success,
and we're right on schedule!
I wanna know how you
managed to get an expensive
camera like this for free.
I hope you're not doing
something crazy
like blackmailing
that poor old guy.
No way! I just explained
our situation to him,
and he gave it to me!
[KYON] If that's what really
happened, tell me what you said.
I want one, too.
[HARUHI] All I did was tell him
that we wanted to shoot a movie.
Then, he just gave me
the camera, no problem.
[KYON]
There's no problem now,
but I have a feeling
there will be later.
Oh, stop worrying so much!
All you have to do
is be my subordinate
and do whatever
I tell you to do.
[laughs]
[HARUHI] Come on! Let's go
to the next store!
[KYON]
I was beginning to understand.
Whenever Haruhi pointed at us,
she was actually pointing
at Miss Asahina.
I think the idea was for Miss
Asahina to be the currency
for all the stuff
Haruhi was getting.
I wonder if I should tell her.
[HARUHI]
Ta-da!
[KYON]
Now, what'd you get?
[HARUHI]
Weapons!
Here.
Ugh, what am I
gonna do with these?!
We're gonna use 'em
for our action scenes.
Nothing's more entertaining
than flashy gun-fighting action!
In fact, I was even thinking we
could blow up a whole building!
Which reminds me,
do you know any place
where we can get some dynamite?
How 'bout that shop
on the corner?
How would I know?
I'm pretty sure you can't
buy it online though.
What am I supposed to do
with all this stuff anyway?
It's too late to go back
to school with it now,
so just take it home!
Don't forget to bring it to the
club room tomorrow though, okay?
Really?
Yeah, really.
[HARUHI] That's her
special SOS Brigade smile,
the one you don't
see in class too often.
When I see that smile,
I know I'll be doing
damage control
after some catastrophe
she's caused.
I'm like the Anti-Straw
Millionaire!
Excuse me?