[KYON]
Walking home after school,
side by side with a girl.
Sure, that sounds like a typical
scene out of some show
about teenage adolescence,
but I'd be lying
if I said I never
dreamed of doing that.
And right now, it looks like
I'm making that dream a reality.
Yeah, so why am I
not happy about it?
[HARUHI]
That way.
Did you say something?
Um, no. Nothing.
[sighs]
[KYON] Pretty soon, we'll be
in front of Nagato's condo.
[HARUHI] Apparently, Asakura
lived here in number 505!
[KYON]
I see.
What're you talkin' about?
See what?
Uh, no, it's nothing.
And by the way, how do you
plan on getting in there?
You got the code for
the door or something?
No, I don't. But I'm sure if we
just wait around long enough--
[gasps]
Well, what're you waiting for?!
I'm telling you, it's strange.
Transferring to Canada
out of nowhere.
And they didn't even tell
anybody their new address.
I know, I heard you already.
Well hang on, 'cause
it gets even stranger.
Asakura didn't go to the junior
high schools in this city
before starting North High.
[KYON]
Well, of course she didn't.
I snooped around and found out
that she came to our school
from a city outside
our school zone.
That's totally suspicious!
It's not like North High's
a famous prep school,
it's just a plain old public
school you can find anywhere.
So why would she wanna
go to our school?
Dunno.
I can't believe it. She lived
really close to the school,
and she lived in a condo.
It's not a monthly deal
like an apartment;
this location's nice
so it's not cheap.
Did she commute from here to
junior high in another city?
[KYON]
I said I don't know.
[HARUHI] It looks like
we have to investigate
how long Asakura's
lived here, too.
What're you doing?
The place is empty.
It's not gonna open.
[KYON] I really think we're
wasting our time here...
[yawns]
Then we're going to
the manager's office.
Do you honestly think they're
just gonna hand over the keys?
No, I'm gonna ask
the manager how long
Asakura lived here. Come on!
Let's just give up and go home.
Even if we find out,
there's nothing we can
really do about it.
Move it!
We're both friends of Miss
Ryoko Asakura who lived here
and we heard she moved
away suddenly.
And we're wondering if you
could help us with something.
We need to get ahold of her,
but she didn't leave
us her address.
Did she happen to tell you
where she was moving?
Also, I was wondering if you
could tell us if you knew
how long Miss
Asakura's lived here.
[KYON] Wow. I wasn't really
expecting her to be so lucid.
[MANAGER]
Hmm... Huuuh?!
[HARUHI] We want to know what
Miss Ryoko Asakura's new address
is, and we want to know
how long she lived here!
Ah, that's right! You mean
Miss Asakura in number 505.
Funny thing about that,
I don't recall seeing
any moving van out front,
but the place was emptied out.
That really surprised me.
Wow, that's strange.
No moving van?
[MANAGER] Don't know
where she moved to either.
I don't know where to forward
any of their mail or packages
that might show up.
It's all bit troubling.
Do you know how long she
lived in number 505?
I'm thinkin' maybe
since three years ago?
Heh, I remember well, because
a pretty young girl came by
with a box of old-fashioned
sweets for me.
[HARUHI] What about her parents?
Did both of them work?
Do you happen to know what
her mother and father
did for a living?
Not a clue. Come to think,
I only saw the girl
every now and again.
And I never saw her parents,
never even said hello to 'em.
The condos here are pretty
expensive, aren't they?
I doubt that anyone would take
out a loan for a place like this
just for their daughter
to live all by herself.
They paid cash. They paid
for the whole thing
up front in cold, hard cash.
I always thought the family
was filthy rich.
[KYON]
Maybe she should be a detective.
She sure knows how
to get answers.
At least I wish I coulda
said goodbye to her.
It's a shame, you know?
By the way, heh, heh,
you're quite a looker,
if you don't mind me sayin' so.
[HARUHI] Thank you very much
for all of your time, sir.
[MANAGER]
Hey, boy.
[KYON]
Hm?
[chuckles] That one's gonna
grow up to be a heck of a catch.
Don't you let her get
away now, y'hear?
Yuki?
[KYON]
Hmm?
Wow, she actually eats food.
I had no idea you lived in this
building. What a coincidence.
[KYON] I really doubt
it's a coincidence.
Have you heard anything about
what happened to Asakura?
You know she transferred
out today, right?
I see. Well, if you find
anything out, let me know.
You got it?
What happened to your glasses?
[KYON] Don't look at me.
I don't know what to say.
Be careful.
[KYON]
Hm...?
[KYON] Great. What do I
have to be careful of now?
[HARUHI]
Let's go!
Uh.
[sighs]
So, what's next? Where are
you planning on going now?
I dunno.
[KYON]
Okay...
Uh, hey. Is it cool
if I go home now?
You know, Kyon, have you
ever realized just how
insignificant your existence
on this planet really is?
[KYON]
Now what is she talking about?
It happened to me,
and I'll never forget it.
Back when I was in the sixth
grade, my whole family
went out to go watch a baseball
game at the stadium.
I didn't really care about
baseball, but I was surprised
by what I saw when we got there.
Everywhere I looked,
I saw people.
On the other side of the
stadium, the people looked
so small, like little
moving grains of rice.
It was so crowded, I thought
that everyone in Japan
had to be packed in there.
So I turned to my
dad and asked him,
"Do you know how many people
are here right now?"
He said since the stadium
was full, probably 50,000.
After the game, the street
was filled with people
and I was really shocked
to see that, too.
To me, it seemed like there
was a ton of people there.
But then, I realized it could
only be a tiny fraction
of all the people in Japan.
When I got home,
I pulled out my calculator.
In Social Studies, I'd learned
the population of Japan
was a hundred-some odd million.
So I divided that by 50,000.
The answer was
one-two-thousandth.
That shocked me even more.
I was only one little person
in that big, crowded stadium
filled with people.
And, believe me, there were
so many people there.
But it was just a handful
of the entire population.
Up till then, I always thought
that I was... I don't know...
...kind of a... special person.
It was fun to be with my family.
I had fun with my classmates.
And the school that
I was going to,
it had just about the most
interesting people anywhere.
But that night,
I realized it wasn't true.
All the stuff we did during
class that I thought was so fun
and cool was probably happening
just like that in classes
in other schools all over Japan.
There was nothing special
about my school at all.
When I realized that,
it suddenly felt like the
whole world around me started
to fade into a dull, gray void.
Brushing my teeth and
going to sleep at night,
waking up and eating
breakfast in the morning,
that stuff happened
all over the place.
They were everyday things
that everybody was doing.
When I thought about it like
that, everything became boring.
If there's really that
many people in the world,
then there had to be someone
who wasn't ordinary.
There had to be someone who was
living an interesting life.
There just had to be.
But why wasn't I that person?
So, that's how I felt till
I finished elementary school.
And then I had
another realization.
I realized fun things
wouldn't come my way
just by waiting for them.
I thought when I got into
junior high, it was time
for me to make a change.
I'd let the world know
I wasn't a girl
who wasn't happy sitting
around waiting,
and I've done my best
to become that person.
But in the end,
nothing happened.
More time went by,
and before I knew it,
I was in high school.
I thought that something
would change.
[KYON] The passing train
gave me a moment
to think about my response.
Should I voice an
opposing view point?
Maybe I should wax
philosophical about her dilemma.
I see...
[KYON]
I must be getting melancholic
if that's the best I
could come up with.
[HARUHI]
I'm going home.
[KYON] The truth is, I'd get
home faster if I went that way,
too. But the way Haruhi was
walking, well, it was like
her back was telling me
not to follow her.
I had no other choice but
to stand there all by myself
until I couldn't see
Haruhi's back anymore.
I wonder what the
hell I'm doing?
[KOIZUMI]
Hello there.
I was thinkin' that
perhaps today I'd
make good on that
promise I made you.
So I've just been hangin' around
out here until you got home.
You're sounding a little
bit like you know
where I've been all day.
Would you mind explaining
that to me.
[KOIZUMI] If it's possible,
do you think you might have
a little time to spare
for me right now?
Is it something to
do with Suzumiya?
It's somethin' to do
with Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON] It's pretty amazing
that this taxi showed up
just when you needed it.
Yeah. Weird.
So the other day, you asked
me to show you some proof
that I'm an ESPer.
You still wanna see it?
That perfect opportunity I was
talkin' about's popped up,
so I thought I'd
have you join me.
Why do we need to go so far
out of town to do this?
We're gonna have to drive a
little ways if you wanna see
my abilities as an ESPer.
It's timing, really.
A certain place,
the right conditions...
So now we're heading out
towards just such a location
and it meets all
the requirements
in exactly the right ways.
Do you still think that Haruhi's
some kind of god or something?
Let me ask you this:
Do you know what the
anthropic principle is?
[KYON]
Nope, never heard of it.
Okay then, here it goes.
Basically, this is the theory
that the universe is
the way it is right
now simply because
human beings could
observe it and determine
that it was the way it is.
So, did you get all that?
I didn't get any of it
How about, I observe,
therefore the universe is.
Or something along those lines.
In other words, on
this particular world,
there are sentient beings
that are called "humans."
Now then, by discovering the
laws of physics in constants,
human beings can observe
the fact that the universe
actually exists at all. When
that happens, the existence
of the universe
becomes apparent.
Therefore, we can say if
the human beings who observe
the universe hadn't actually
evolved as far as they did,
then there wouldn't be any
observations, and the universe
wouldn't have anyone to
acknowledge its existence.
So it wouldn't really matter
if the universe existed or not.
The universe is because
human beings know it is.
Anyway, that's the reasoning
from the human perspective.
[KYON]
You're kidding, right?
I mean, with or without humans,
the universe is still
the universe.
Well, that's also correct.
Therefore, the anthropic
principle isn't anything more
than a speculative theory.
However, this theory does bring
up an interesting dilemma.
Why was the universe created
in such a way that human beings
could survive in it?
It would only take a slight
change in the gravitational
constant or particle mass ratio
for the universe to not allow
a planet like
the Earth to exist.
Okay, you sound like one of
those pamphlets from some
kooky religion that's into
science and technology.
Actually, I don't really believe
that humans were created
by a god or some
omnipotent being.
With all I've seen, something
like that doesn't make sense.
I say that, but I
still have doubts.
About what?
Sometimes I get the feeling that
we're all just a bunch of clowns
standing on our tiptoes at
the edge of a great abyss.
[chuckles] No, I'm just kidding.
[KYON] Look, I don't understand
a thing you just said.
The reason I went into the whole
anthropic principle thing
was to draw a comparison.
I haven't even gotten
to Miss Suzumiya yet.
And that's another thing.
Why are you and Nagato
and Miss Asahina all
so obsessed with Haruhi?
Well, I can't speak
for the others,
but I think she's charming.
Anyway, let's get
back to business.
I was wondering if you
remember the stuff I once
explained to you about how
the world may have in fact
been created by Miss Suzumiya.
Although it's annoying as hell,
yeah, I do remember
you saying that.
She has the power to turn
anything she wishes for
into a reality.
Oh, come on, you can't seriously
believe that's true.
Miss Suzumiya was positive
that aliens existed,
and then she wished that
there was such a thing.
That's why Yuki Nagato's here.
She wanted to meet people
from the future,
so she wished for that, too.
And that's why Mikuru
Asahina showed up here.
And as for myself, she wished
for ESPers to be a reality,
and, lo and behold,
here I am at your service, sir.
Like I said, how do you
know all this anyway?
[KOIZUMI]
Well, about three years ago--
[KYON] I'm a little sick of
hearing about this
three years ago crap.
Three years ago, and
without any warning,
I just knew I had these
powers and I also knew
how I should use them.
And I wasn't alone.
There were other people
who had the same experience
as me at the same time.
And get this, all of us
knew that Haruhi Suzumiya
was the reason for it.
I can't explain why.
It was just something
that all of us knew.
All right, I'll give you
the benefit of the doubt,
but I really can't see Haruhi
doing that kind of stuff.
[KOIZUMI] At first, we couldn't
believe it ourselves either.
No one could wrap their heads
around the possibility
that, thanks to one girl,
the whole universe changed
or maybe it was created.
And on top of all that, it's
like there's nothing here
that's special enough
to hold her interest.
That's the scary thing about it.
Why scary?
[KOIZUMI]
I told you.
If you had the power to create
the universe at will,
you'd also have the power
to destroy this world.
Then you could rebuild it
into whatever you wanted.
If that really happened,
it would mean the end
of everything as we know it.
Although if it does happen,
and we'd have no way
of knowing it even
happened, then again,
maybe something like that
has happened before.
You never know.
Perhaps the universe has
been destroyed and rebuilt
lots of times already.
[KYON] Look, why don't you tell
Haruhi what you really are.
I'm sure if she found out
that ESPers were real,
she'd be ecstatic.
Then maybe she wouldn't think
about changing the world.
[KOIZUMI] Well, there's
a problem with that.
If Miss Suzumiya finds
out about us ESPers
and then starts thinkin'
our powers are like
some common occurrence,
the world would be
knee deep in ESPers.
Every law of physics
would get twisted up
like a garden hose.
The entire universe would
fall into chaos.
[KYON] If you guys exist
because Haruhi wished it,
why isn't she aware of it?
I mean, don't you
think that's strange?
[KOIZUMI]
Not really.
There's the part of
her that wished for
aliens, ESPers, and time
travelers to be real,
but she's also got a practical
side that thinks
those things are impossible.
She's conflicted
between the two.
Yes, she does and says
things that are eccentric,
but in reality, Miss Suzumiya's
just an ordinary human
with a good sense of what's
real and what's not.
In junior high, her energy
was like a sandstorm,
but in the past few months,
it's started to calm down.
I'd prefer it if
she stayed calm.
But now, we need to face
the fact that she's
creating a new tornado.
[KYON]
What d'you mean?
Hate to say it,
but it's your fault.
What do I have to do with this?
What're you talkin' about?
You're the one
that gave her the idea to
form this strange club.
Because of the conversation
she had with you,
Haruhi decided that
she'd create a club
filled with all sorts of
weird people, didn't she?
Therefore, you are
responsible for this.
And because of that,
a member from each of
the three groups that
are interested in what
Haruhi Suzumiya is doing are
now conveniently gathered
together in one place.
[KYON]
So I'm the scapegoat.
[KOIZUMI] Well, actually,
there's more to it than that.
[KOIZUMI] I hate to say
this after draggin' you
all the way out here, but
if you'd prefer to go back,
it's not too late.
[KYON]
You gotta be kidding me.
All right then, so could you do
me a favor and close your eyes?
It'll only take a
couple of seconds.
[KYON]
Hmm?
[gasps]
[KYON]
Do you have to hold my hand?
[KOIZUMI]
Okay, open 'em.
The gap between dimensions.
Separate from the world we know,
completely closed space.
And in the middle
of this crosswalk
is the wall for
this closed space.
It's about five kilometers wide,
and normally there isn't any
physical way of
entering this space.
But that's one of
the powers I have.
That is, when the
conditions are right.
If you can picture a dome
that's been plopped down
over the city, well,
we're standing in it.
As we're in here, talking,
life goes on as normal
in the world outside the space.
And normal folks wandering
in here, well,
that doesn't happen too often.
Now, closed spaces created
completely at random.
Sometimes they pop up
every other day.
And sometimes you won't see
one for a couple of months.
One things for sure though,
whenever Miss Suzumiya
gets emotionally unstable,
it creates a space
like this somewhere.
I can sense when closed
space is created,
and I know where to go to
find the door to get in.
My powers aren't limited
to finding these things
and getting into them.
You could say that my power
somehow reflect upon the things
within Miss Suzumiya's
consciousness.
So if this closed place
is a pimple that appears
on Miss Suzumiya's spirit, we
ESPers are the acne medication.
You know, your metaphors
are hard to understand.
[KOIZUMI sighs]
Yeah, I get that a lot.
But then, you sure
are something.
I mean, here you are,
seeing all this,
but you don't seem surprised.
I've seen a lot of strange
things already.
Well, it looks like
it's starting.
Please, take a look behind you.
[KYON]
Hmm?
[gasps]
[KOIZUMI] When Miss Suzumiya's
irritation level
gets to a certain point,
these giants suddenly appear.
I think it's a form of
stress relief for her
with those things acting
out on her behalf
and destroying stuff.
I mean, she can't
go causing riots
or anything in the real world,
so she creates a closed
space and she's free
to unleash her fury inside it.
Don't you think that's logical?
I mean, that thing
shouldn't be able
to support its own weight.
It seems to transcend the
laws of physics, doesn't it?
Even if you brought in an army
unit in to fire rockets at it,
it still wouldn't
stop that thing.
So you mean that thing just
keeps tearing stuff up?!
Not quite.
Have a look over there.
[KOIZUMI]
Other ESPers.
They're just like me, people
that hunt down the giants
created and powered
by Miss Suzumiya.
Stay here. It's time
for me to go help out.
[KYON grunts]
[KYON] I can't believe
this is happening.
Sorry to make you wait.
Oh, there's something
else I wanna show you.
Last thing, I promise.
I don't think anything's
gonna top that.
Once us ESPers get
rid of the giant,
the bubble of closed
space disintegrates,
and it's quite the spectacle.
[car horn honks]
[KOIZUMI]
So, now do you understand?
[KYON]
Uh... no.
We have a name for
that giant you saw.
We call them "Shinjin,"
a man that's made by god.
The Shinjin are linked to
Miss Suzumiya's metal state
and so are we. Stop me if
this starts to get confusing.
When a closed space is created,
the Shinjin rise up
and take the form of giants.
That's when I get to unleash
my supernatural powers.
However, I can only use them
within the confines
of the closed space.
Right now, sitting in this cab,
I don't have any powers at all.
You're probably wondering
why I've been given
these powers, right?
I guess it would've been okay
for anybody to have 'em.
I just happened to
be the one chosen.
And as for the Shinjin,
we can't leave them alone
to do what they want. The
reason is, that the more stuff
the Shinjin get to destroy, the
bigger the closed space becomes.
That space we were just in?
Believe it or not, that was
one of the smaller ones.
If we left it alone,
it'd keep on growing,
getting bigger and bigger
until it covered the world.
If that happens, the world ends.
The gray void of the closed
space would replace
the world we live in now.
But how do you know it
would happen like that?
I don't know how I know,
I just know that
I know, you know?
And the same goes
for everyone else
that belongs to
the organization.
If we don't do something
about all this,
the world doesn't stand
a chance at all.
It's such a bother.
So please, keep an eye on
Miss Suzumiya's behavior.
Her mental state's been stable
for a while, but it looks
like it's starting
to get active again.
Things like today haven't
happened in a long time.
Even if I do keep
an eye on Haruhi,
don't you think I'm a little
out of my league here?
Hey now, don't sell
yourself so short.
If it were up to me, I'd let
you handle all the stuff
by yourself, 'cause if there's
anyone that I trust,
it'd be you.
But, there's many different
opinions among us,
and things are definitely
complicated.
[KYON] Koizumi tells me to keep
an eye on Haruhi's behavior,
and for some reason, Nagato
tells me to be careful.
Even though both
of them warned me,
I really didn't think anything
would happen right away.
If I could see into the future
and know that the very next day
I'd be in the middle of one
of the hairiest situations
ever in my life,
I'm sure I wouldn't
have been as calm
as I was right then.