[KYON] Something's wrong...
That's what it felt like anyway.
[KYON] I didn't care about
the baseball game on TV
because it was between
schools from another town.
But, because I tend to
symphatize with underdogs,
I ended up rooting
for the losing team.
And it was right about then,
that I suddenly got the
feeling Haruhi was gonna call.
[phone rings]
Your phone's ringing, Kyon.
I know; you don't
have to tell me.
[HARUHI]
Hey, you're free, right? Good.
Meet us at 2:00 in front of
the station. And don't be late!
[dial tone]
[KYON] I didn't even have
a chance to say anything.
[phone rings]
[KYON]
Now what?
[HARUHI]
I forgot to tell you,
make sure to bring your swim
trunks and some money, too.
Oh, wait, wait. And your bike.
Definitely bring your bike.
That's it. Over and out!
--[dial tone]
--[KYON] Mhm.
That was weird.
It was like I knew what
Haruhi was gonna say
before she even said anything.
Hang on... Actually,
it felt more like
we'd had the exact same
conversation before,
like déjà vu or something.
[COMMENTATOR]
And the pitch...
[metal clink]
[KYON'S SISTER gasps]
[COMMENTATOR]
It's a big, fat hit!
[KYON]
Summer's almost over...
[HARUHI]
You're late again, Kyon!
Where is your motivation?
[KYON]
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
No worries. I just
got here, too.
[HARUHI] Now that we're all
present and accounted for,
we can go!
Where to?
To the public swimming pool!
Where do ya think?
[KYON] That figures...
considering the stuff I brought.
We've got lots and lots of
summer vacation-y things
to do during our summer break!
But, we've only so
much time because
once it's gone,
it's gone for good!
So we're gonna do everything
we can, while we can
during our only summer
as tenth graders!
And for starters, we're riding
the bikes to the pool!
Okay. Did everyone
ride their bikes today?
No... The only bikes
we have to ride over
are the ones you and I brought.
[KYON]
Huh?
All right, Kyon! You can't
let Koizumi beat you!
Come on! Full speed ahead!
[KYON]
No ESP allowed!
[HARUHI] Come on, guys,
hurry up and park your bikes.
Kyon! We're trying to
have fun, so stop acting tired!
[KYON]
And whose fault is that?!
[HARUHI]
Mmm, can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes
it feel like summer!
[HARUHI gasps]
Hurry and get in!
Come on, the water's warm!
It's perfect!
[KYON] Can't she see
the "no diving" signs?
They're everywhere!
Well, that looks like fun.
Don't you think?
I mean, seeing her enjoy
the day in a normal fashion.
It's a rather
charming sight, isn't it?
And as long as Miss Suzumiya's
having a good time here,
we don't have to worry about
any earth-shattering events.
[KYON]
I hope you're right.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
It's probably my imagination.
Come on, let's go and
have some fun, too.
[MIKURU giggles]
[KYON] It's so bitter!
May I have another?
[KYON] That's weird. It's like
I've seen this before.
Nagato... sitting all alone,
looking bored...
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
[KYON] Yeah... And then Haruhi
shows up, and she says...
So, these two guys are
my brigade members.
They do what I say.
So if you want something,
you can ask them!
Time for some fun!
Let's play dodgeball
in the pool!
We're coming!
[KYON] Oh, well.
Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
[HARUHI] I've been thinking of
some fun things we could do!
Check it out!
[KYON]
What is that?
It's a schedule of
how we're gonna
spend the rest of
our summer vacation!
I realized something...
We've only got two more weeks
of summer vacation left to go!
That fact totally blew me away.
We've done a lot of cool things
but we've only got so much time,
and there's a bajillion
more things left to do!
So I say, we gotta
pick up the pace!
[KYON] We've got two
weeks to do all that?!
Mikuru, is there anything
else you wanna do?
[MIKURU]
Huh?
Um... I think I'd like to
try goldfish scooping?
[HARUHI] Okay!
Goldfish scooping, it is...
Could I see the list you made?
[KOIZUMI]
Hm.
Okay, thanks.
[HARUHI]
We'll start the list tomorrow!
Do you guys know if there's a
bon festival happening anywhere?
Or even a firework show?
I could check around for those.
I'll call you if I find one.
Don't forget about
goldfish scooping.
After all, it's Mikuru's
only request.
[KOIZUMI]
Okay, I'll get right on it.
That's it for today! See ya!
I'll be going, too.
[MIKURU]
Me too. Bye!
[KYON]
Nagato!
Hey, sorry, it's nothing
important or anything...
So, how have you been?
Is everything okay?
It is.
[KYON]
Oh! Good!
What was that all about?
Why'd I want to talk to her?
[ANNOUNCER] May I have
your attention, please.
We have a lost child...
[KYON]
A bon festival, huh?
Figures it'd be so crowded.
[KYON gasps]
That tower... Those vendors...
I haven't been to a
bon festival in a while,
but it feels like I
just went to one.
[HARUHI]
Mikuru!
They have goldfish scooping over
there, just like you wanted!
Come on, you're gonna
catch a ton!
[MIKURU whimpering]
Okay...
Do you wanna go
scoop some fish, too?
We could have a contest.
Think I'll pass.
How 'bout you, Nagato?
You wanna go get some food?
[KYON] I didn't know you
were into this kinda stuff.
I got it!
[NAGATO]
No.
That one.
[VENDOR]
Sure, 800 yen!
[KYON] I wish she would've
let me buy that for her...
It's the least I could do
after all she's done for us.
[HARUHI]
Thirteen fish!
It's like the most
unbelievable haul ever!
But, I don't have any
place to put 'em all.
So I just kept one, and I
gave another one to Mikuru!
Go ahead and have one,
but only one!
[KYON]
Thanks.
Hey, Yuki, what's up with
the mask you got there?
I bought it.
Oh... Okay.
[giggles]
[sizzling]
[KYON] It was summer,
and summer vacation.
I guess that's why I
wanted to forget about it.
Truth was, I couldn't
ignore it any longer.
Haruhi, I don't want
to spoil your fun,
but did you finish
your homework?
Are you kidding?
That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it
in like three days.
[KYON]
Three days?!
[HARUHI] You have to
get rid of that junk first,
so you can spend the
rest of your summer
having fun and not
worrying about it!
[KYON] Why does she
have to be so smart?
The folks upstairs
weren't terribly fair
when they were divvying
up the stats for us.
You guys! Tomorrow,
we're gonna go catch some bugs!
And the prize for whoever
catches the most
bugs is gonna be...
...um... I know! They get to be
brigade leader for a whole day!
[KYON]
No thanks!
That sounds like a lot of fun!
Can we catch just
any random bug?
Um... No... Only cicadas!
In fact, I'm calling it
the SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest!
[KYON] The next day was
beautiful, sunny, and bright.
In fact, it was the
perfect day for us
to have our SOS Brigade's
cicada catching contest.
[KYON yelling]
[KYON]
That's not a cicada.
I-It's a yanbaru
long-armed scarab!
Although everyone caught bugs
the best way they knew how,
the winner of the
contest ended up being...
You guessed it, Haruhi.
It's important to
follow the spirit of
catch and release
with these guys.
You never know,
if we let 'em go now,
they might come back
and return the favor!
[KYON] What could
a cicada do for me,
even if it did come back?
[HARUHI] Hurry!
Go back to the mountains!
[cicada's chirping]
[KYON]
I sorta feel like Pandora,
when she opened her box.
[MIKURU]
Welcome to our store!
[KYON]
We met the next day,
even though we had absolutely
no idea what was going on.
Our confusion continued
as we stood outside
the local supermarket,
wearing frog costumes
and handing out balloons.
It's a living.
[MIKURU whimpers]
I feel like Unit Zero after
it got hit by that beam.
Hey, guys! Awesome job today!
[KYON] What's with
the special treatment?!
You're the best!
The manager's super grateful
for all the hard work.
[KYON] Who cares how grateful
he is? What about our pay?
There it is!
Huh?!
I've had my eye on this
little guy for a long time now.
--[giggles]
--[KYON] We worked in the sun,
sweat pouring down
our foreheads...
...for that?!
We'll keep him in the
club room as a souvenir.
Oh, and Mikuru,
you have my permission
to wear him whenever you want.
Help yourself, okay?
[MIKURU]
Sure! Uh...
[KYON]
Yeah? What?
Oh, it's nothing.
[KYON]
Don't stare at me.
Come on, Mikuru!
You're the cutest
little froggy ever!
Put it back on,
you know you want to!
Watch the popsicle, ladies.
[phone rings]
[KYON]
Later that night,
my peaceful slumber was
interrupted by a phone call.
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] The number you have
dialed is no longer...
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON screams]
What the heck?!
[MIKURU whimpering]
Kyon...
Miss Asahina, is that you?
[MIKURU sobbing]
Yes... It's me...
Something... really bad...
I don't know... Wha...
What's wrong?
[KOIZUMI]
Hello, it's Koizumi.
How about you tell
me what you're doing
with Miss Asahina in
the middle of the night?
[KOIZUMI]
We have a situation here.
Would it be possible for
you to come meet us now?
Miss Asahina! Is everything
okay? What happened?
[MIKURU sobbing]
Oh, Kyon! I-I-I can't
go back to the future...!
[KOIZUMI]
I'll explain it the best I can.
Currently, we're stuck in a time
loop that seems to be infinite.
[KYON] It's hard to
believe you're serious
with you sitting there,
smiling like that.
I mean, come on, Koizumi.
Do you have any idea
what you just said?
Yes, of course, I do. Much more
than I want to, believe me.
Earlier, I was having a
chat with Miss Asahina.
[KYON] Next time, you guys
are chatting, call me!
And then suddenly, we came
to the conclusion that
there was something a little off
about the current flow of time.
But the truth is,
Miss Asahina discovered it.
Thanks to her, my suspicions
were confirmed.
What suspicions?
[KOIZUMI]
Hm.
We're currently stuck
in a time loop,
re-living the same
period of time,
over and over again.
[KYON]
Yeah, you already said that.
[KOIZUMI] We've been
repeating every day between
August the 17th
through the 31st.
We're in the middle
of what seems to be
an endless summer vacation.
Well, at least it's summer
vacation anyway...
It's a never-ending,
endless summer vacation.
The future doesn't exist
in this world anymore.
Time stops at September the 1st.
And who's gonna
believe such a thing?
Well, for starters,
we were sort of hoping that
you would believe it.
[MIKURU]
Um...
I think I can try to explain it.
Okay, here it goes...
Because I have to
classified information,
I used classified information
to get in touch with the future.
The thing is, I haven't gotten
any classified information
for about a week now.
And that's kind of weird.
I was so surprised,
I classified information.
I really did.
But it was classified
information.
I don't know what to do.
[KYON]
What about those closed spaces
you were talking about before?
Maybe we're trapped
in one of those.
No, it's not one of those.
A section of time has been
torn away from time-space.
At exactly midnight on August
the 31st, everything will reset.
Then time reverts straight back
to the morning of
August the 17th.
That's the process.
What about our-- No, wait.
What about the whole
world's memories?
Their memories are reset.
Everyone's memory starts
over from the beginning.
Perfect, another
problem involving time.
I guess that figures when
there's a time traveler around.
No, Miss Asahina didn't
have anything to do with this.
[KYON]
Then, what's causing it?
It's Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON sighs]
I'm sure she doesn't
even realize it.
I think subconsciously,
she wants to
have summer vacation
last forever.
You're kidding!
You're telling me she still
hasn't had enough fun?
Yeah, that's what I think.
[KYON sighs]
[KOIZUMI] Perhaps she feels
there's something else that
needs to happen before
our summer vacation
can really be over.
[KYON sighs] You seem like
you're kind of enjoying this.
Do you wanna tell me why?
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
Please don't take that
the wrong way, it's just...
This explains the feelings
of déjà vu I've been having.
But, now that I think about it,
those feelings were most likely
the residue of my memories
from all the other instances
where time had been reset.
So, are we the only ones?
Or can other people
feel this happening, too?
It doesn't seem that way.
You and I are exceptions
to the rule though.
[KOIZUMI] The only people who
can sense this strangeness
are the ones closest
to Miss Suzumiya.
But, what about Haruhi?
Does she have any idea about
the stuff that's been going on?
No, I don't think
she knows about it.
Besides, it would be
very bad for us if she did.
But there's someone else who
isn't affected by the time loop,
or the feelings of déjà vu
we've been experiencing.
This person remembers
everything that's happened
since this started.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
Is that true?
It is.
[KYON]
Then... you remember everything?
I can.
[KYON] Okay then, how many
times has this happened so far?
This would be
15,521 times so far.
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred twenty-one times?
Wait... What do you
mean 15,521 times?
And... you're being
completely serious?
I am.
So then, you're saying that
we've done the exact same things
that many times,
every single time?
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,521 repetitions,
we did not attend
a bon festival the 2,391st
time and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon festival
but did not go to
a goldfish scooping
booth exactly 437 times.
We obtained part-time
jobs 9,048 times,
and performed six
different types of jobs.
In addition to handing
out balloons,
we worked as movers,
cashiers, we handed out--
[KYON]
Okay! I got it...
[KYON] Fifteen thousand
five-hundred twenty-one times...
That's what Nagato said.
Okay... So... times two weeks...
That's, uh...
about... 595 years.
She's the only one of us who
remembers everything we've done.
And she's had to repeat those
same things over and over again.
Nagato...
What's it like to re-live the
same things that many times?
That's gotta be the
craziest story ever.
[HARUHI]
I wonder if they're real.
[KYON]
What's real?
[HARUHI]
Martians.
[KYON]
I kind of hope they aren't.
I can't see anyone on
the surface right now,
but I bet they're a
reserved race of beings
who have to live underground.
Whenever us humans are
finally able to land on Mars,
I'm sure the Martians'll pop out
from wherever they're hiding,
and say something like,
"Welcome to Mars!"
[KYON] I don't think
they should pop out.
[HARUHI]
Ugh, this is boring.
I'm gonna look for
some UFOs now.
[KYON]
That night, we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony
of Nagato's apartment,
since her place
had the best view.
Koizumi brought the telescope.
[KYON] I wish I knew what
else she wants to do.
Well, that's
the question, isn't it?
If we knew the answer,
we could solve this thing.
I have an idea we
can try if you want.
What if someone were to suddenly
grab Miss Suzumiya from behind,
and then whispered, "I love
you," right into her ear?
And who's gonna be
doing the whispering?
Is there anyone who could
play that role other than you?
[KYON]
Hmm... Yeah, no thanks.
All right then,
how 'bout if I do it?
Of course, I'm kidding.
I don't think I
could pull that off.
And besides,
it would just confuse
Miss Suzumiya in the end.
[chuckles]
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato.
You knew about this time loop
before Miss Asahina
figured it out, didn't you?
I did.
So then, how come you
didn't say anything about it?
[NAGATO]
My function is to observe.
[KYON]
I see...
We kept chugging along,
doing all kinds of
summer vacation things.
We went to a real firework show,
and we even signed up for
a goby fishing tournament.
We went to the batting cages,
we watched some movies,
went to the beach,
bowling, karaoke.
Oh yeah, we were
always doing something.
And the whole time,
all I could think was that
none of it was going to
be enough for Haruhi.
[KYON]
But, what could I do about it?
Nothing.
So, I just bit my
lip and watched
as the last days of summer...
vacation went by...
[KYON wretches]
And then, before I knew it,
August the 30th was here.
[HARUHI] That's it. We've done
everything on our list.
Hey! Don't mess that up!
Hmm... But now I'm
wondering if we did enough.
Oh, well. Yeah, I guess
we did do a lot of stuff...
Unless there's something
else you guys wanna do?
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON gasping]
Oh! Okay, then.
I guess we did pretty much
everything we set out to do,
so that's good enough.
[KYON]
No, it's not.
You're still not satisfied.
That's it then!
We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can go ahead
and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the
club room on Monday!
[KYON grunts]
[MIKURU gasps]
[KYON]
Wait, Haruhi.
That's it then!
We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can go ahead
and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the
club room on Monday!
[KYON]
I can't let Haruhi leave.
[MIKURU gasps]
[KYON]
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up re-living
the past two weeks
again and again for a
thousand more times!
That's it then!
We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can go ahead
and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the
club room on Monday!
[KYON]
What should I do?
What should I say?
[MIKURU gasps]
[KYON] There must have been a
clue in something Haruhi said...
But what was it?
What's she been
saying all this time?
I don't know...
I can't... remember...
That's it then!
We're all done for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can go ahead
and take the day off now, okay?
I'll see you guys at the
club room on Monday!
[KYON]
Whatever... It doesn't matter.
It's August the 31st.
And I still haven't
touched my homework.
[KYON]
Who cares?
There's no point in doing it.
I mean, we're just gonna keep
re-living the last
couple of weeks.
[KYON] Whatever happens next,
whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me
will have to deal with it.
[clock ticking]