[KYON] Okay, I wanna know what
you've got up your sleeve.
[KOIZUMI] Nothing.
Really, there's nothing.
I know that the
organization doesn't have
anything to do with this,
although, I did
report it to them.
No, we're just going
on a little retreat.
[KYON] A little retreat
that you set up.
I'm just making sure
nothing funny's going on.
[KOIZUMI] Miss Suzumiya
was interested because
it's a deserted island
that's privately owned.
She said it was a closed
circle or something.
[KYON]
Okay, what's a closed circle?
[KOIZUMI]
Like in mysteries,
it's a situation
where all contact
with the outside world
has been cut off.
[KYON] Like a cabin in the
mountains during a blizzard,
or someone who can't get
back to civilization because
a typhoon destroyed the bridge.
[KOIZUMI] Exactly. A person or
group of people get trapped
because of their surroundings.
In other words,
they get closed in.
[KYON] And how does that tie in
to this retreat we're taking?
[KOIZUMI] We're going
to a deserted island.
It's the perfect
close-circle setting
when you think about it.
All we need is a storm
to whip up around us
and--voila! Much better
than a cabin in a blizzard.
[KYON] You might be wondering
why I'm chatting with Koizumi
on the deck of a ship
in the middle of the ocean.
This all started as I was
recovering from getting
my final exams back.
In other words: Black Monday.
On that fateful day, the
SOS Brigade had a meeting.
Good, everyone's here.
Now, today's meeting
is super important.
If any of you happened
to show up after me,
I was thinking of making that
person "it" whenever we play
"Kick the Can" forever.
[KYON] Naturally, I had
no idea we were having
an important meeting today.
I've decided during the summer
break, the SOS Brigade's
going on its very first retreat!
Going on a retreat?
[HARUHI]
Yep! Retreat.
[KYON] What good is that
gonna do any of us?
And Koizumi's already
planned our destination.
Correct. It just so happens
that I have a distant relative
who is incredibly wealthy.
He has so much money, that he
actually bought his very own
deserted island and built
his summer house on it.
In fact, the construction was
finished on it not too long ago.
[marker squeaking]
Koizumi, get ready
to hit the roof!
For your distinguished service
and dedication to the brigade,
I'm promoting you
to the rank of...
...Deputy Chief!
I gladly accept.
[marker squeaking]
No, I'm not jealous...
We'll have a luxurious three
nights and four days on...
...a deserted island! And I'm
sure we're going to find
something very interesting
waiting for us there!
In fact, I've
already figured out
what my role in
this adventure is!
[KOIZUMI] Now then, let's think
about detectives for a minute.
The great detectives in
mystery novels always seem
to find themselves
getting involved in
one incomprehensible
situation after another.
Why do you think that is?
[KYON] Because if they didn't,
you wouldn't have a story.
[KOIZUMI]
That's right. No story.
Their cases are
entirely fiction.
They exist only in the
surreal world of the story.
Although, maybe it's better
if we don't get too wrapped up
in a metafictional
conversation just yet.
I mean, after all, Miss Suzumiya
seems pretty gung-ho
about throwing herself
into a world like that.
[KYON]
Come to think of it,
she created the SOS
Brigade to do just that.
If you're in search
of surreal happenings
like the kind in mystery novels,
you need to go someplace
that has the right environment
for that kind of thing.
When you think about it, that's
how every single one of the
great detectives in fiction
got involved in their cases.
Yeah, but there's no way
we'd just stumble
across a case that easy.
[KOIZUMI] True, nothing
ever happens in reality
like it does in stories.
However, the island we're
heading for right now
is a spot that everyone
in the world would think
the perfect place for a
gruesome murder mystery.
[KYON]
Everyone in the world, huh?
That's a heck of a world
you got there, sport.
Look at it this way:
Wherever a great detective goes,
a strange case is practically
guaranteed to happen.
See, it says if all great
detectives have a kind of
supernatural power that attracts
all their cases to them.
Are you sane?
[KOIZUMI] I always act with
a reasonable amount of sanity.
All that stuff about great
detectives, closed circles
and stuff aren't my personal
views on the subject.
I was merely pointing out the
way Miss Suzumiya was thinking.
In other words, well,
she wants to be one.
[HARUHI]
Hm...
[KOIZUMI]
A great detective.
This one!
So close!
[KYON] What's close?
We're playing old maid.
Hurry! Next one!
--Too bad.
--[giggles]
Hey, do you wanna
know something?
My big brother Kyon
tried to leave me at home.
[KYON] That's because I
didn't intend to bring you
in the first place.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[giggles]
[KYON'S SISTER sobs]
No!
Well, we're all happy
you're here now.
Yay!
She won't be any
trouble, I promise.
Mm-hm!
[KYON] Thanks to Miss Asahina's
smile, the kid was off the hook.
[HARUHI] How much longer
till we get there?
[KOIZUMI] It'll take about
six hours by ferry.
Then, an acquaintance will
be waiting to pick us up
when we arrive at the port.
From there, we'll board
a private cruiser
and it'll be another
hour on the water.
A deserted island with a
towering mansion will be
waiting for us at
the end of our trip.
I've never actually been there,
so it'll be interesting
to see what the
mansion looks like.
I bet it'll be a
really strange building.
Hey, do you know the name of
the architect who built it?
[KYON]
Why do you care?
Never really thought
to ask about that.
[KYON'S LITTLE SISTER]
Yay! I'm out first!
Amazing!
[KOIZUMI] Come to think of it,
I did hear the architect
they commissioned to design
it was somewhat famous.
[KYON]
Perfect. "Somewhat" famous.
For starters, if the
mansion is anything
like what Haruhi's expecting,
I'm sure it's totally weird.
It'll probably look like
something Antoni Gaudi built
after drinking himself stupid
and staying up for
three days straight.
[HARUHI] An island. A mansion.
It's the ideal location
for the SOS Brigade's
summer retreat.
Hm...
Woo-hoo! I'm the
third to get out!
How 'bout the loser has to
buy drinks for everyone else?
I'll take a can of
100% fruit juice, please.
And I want some cola.
And I'll be having
the royal milk tea.
[KYON]
Hey, you haven't won yet, buddy.
Yep, deserted islands are
all about weird happenings.
[KYON] I hope nothing happens,
I hope nothing happens...
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
I'm not too sure about that.
Whether or not anything
weird actually happens...
Hm...
...I'm hoping that
this trip will at least
be a fun one for us all.
Uh.
Ah! Ha-ha!
Hey, Mikuru, Little Sister,
let's go up to the deck!
Maybe we'll see a monster
squid or something.
Sure!
Squid, squid!
[KYON]
If a giant squid shows up,
Nagato'll have to deal with it.
[KYON]
Oh brother...
[HARUHI] You dork, are you
sleeping? Come on, wake up!
Are you just gonna sleep
through our entire trip?
[MIKURU giggles] I just took
a picture of you waking up.
And I took a couple
of you sleeping.
You were sound asleep,
weren't you?
[KYON] Huh? Really? Why would
Miss Asahina wanna take pictures
of me sleeping? Maybe she
wants to put a picture of me
in a cute frame, keep it next
to her bed, and every night,
just before she drifts
off to sleep, she--
[HARUHI]
What's with the goofy face?
You might wanna stop 'cause
you look like a moron.
I've temporarily given Mikuru
the responsibility of being
the SOS Brigade's photographer!
It's important to
maintain a record
of the brigade's activities
for future generations.
But I decide what
pictures to take.
Why would anybody care what
I look like when I'm sleeping
or when I'm waking up?
While you're sleeping,
the rest of us are on
an important mission, and
I'm gonna use the pictures
of you loafing as a warning to
future generations. You got it?
For a lowly member to lie around
snoring while his leader
is awake is against
morals, orders,
--and the rules of the brigade.
--[ferry horn blares]
[HARUHI]
We're movin' out, people!
A mysterious island awaits us!
[KYON]
Mysterious island indeed.
[KYON] It's not Panorama Island
or Infant Island, is it?
I hope this island doesn't
float away or start to swim.
That'd ruin my day.
[KOIZUMI]
It'll be all right.
It's just your
typical desert island.
Believe me, you can relax
because there aren't any
monsters or mad
scientist anywhere.
I promise you. In fact,
I'll guarantee it.
[KYON] Guarantee it all you
want, I still don't trust you.
[KOIZUMI] Mr. Arakawa! It's been
a while since I last saw you!
[KOIZUMI] Ms. Mori! Thank you
for coming to meet us.
I'm sorry for
troubling you both.
Now, I'd like to
introduce the two of you
to my incomparable
group of friends.
[ARAKAWA] The boat we'll be
taking is right over here.
It should only take us
about a half an hour or so
to reach the master's island.
My apologies in advance
for any inconvenience.
You're kidding!
I don't mind at all!
The more remote
it is, the better!
Another half hour?
Take as long as you need!
A deserted island in
the middle of the ocean's
exactly what I'm looking for!
Hey, you two should be
totally excited about this.
This island's got a mansion
and a suspicious-looking
butler and maid!
What's with you guys?
I bet you'd maybe find
two islands like this
in Japan, tops.
[KYON]
There aren't even two.
Oh, wow, that's so amazing!
I'm really looking
forward to this.
Wow!
[KYON]
I wonder if Miss Asahina
is trying to pick
up some maidisms
from Ms. Mori. She's looking
at her so intensely.
So does the house on the island
have some kind of cool name?
[MORI]
I'm sorry?
"The House of Black Death,"
"Lyra Manor," "Kouketsu Castle"?
The mansion has to have
a name like that, right?
No, it doesn't.
Maybe it's got a dungeon
full of funky contraptions
where the architect
died unnaturally,
or a room where,
if you sleep in it,
you die a horrible death, right?
No, there isn't.
[KYON]
Way to kill the mood.
[HARUHI] Hey, does the master
of the house wear a mask
'cause he's
horribly disfigured?
Or maybe there's three
psychotic sister living there.
Or maybe,
everyone's disappeared!
No, not at all.
At least, not yet, anyway.
But there's a good chance
something weird like that'll
happen at some point, right?
There's always a
possibility, yes.
Wow, I think I see it!
Is that the mansion?
[ARAKAWA]
Yes, that would be it.
[HARUHI sighs]
It looks so normal...
Someone's waving at us.
Who's that? He looks too young
to be the master of the house.
He's also been invited
to stay a few days.
That's mister Yutaka Tamaru,
the master's younger brother.
I remember meeting
him once before.
Thanks for the heads up.
You think you could let us know
about these things
ahead of time?
This is the first I've ever
heard about any other guests.
[YUTAKA]
Welcome!
[doorbell rings]
Ah, welcome, everyone.
On behalf of my colleagues,
I would like to thank you
for inviting us to your home.
It's truly an honor to be able
to stay in such a grand estate
as yours, sir. We appreciate
your kindness and generosity.
My, oh my. I have to say
you're quite different
from what Itsuki's told me.
Indeed, I think I was expecting
someone who was more direct.
You were?
It's really cool to
meet you, Mr. Master!
But let's cut to the chase;
has anything strange ever
happened in this house?
What about the island? You hear
any story from the locals?
Do they have a spooky
name for the island?
Are they afraid to come near it?
That's the kind of
stuff I'm in to!
[laughs]
Sounds like you have
quite a hobby there.
Although, I've yet to see
anything strange happen here.
Construction on the
house was finished
the day before yesterday.
And as for the island,
I don't recall anyone
saying it was haunted.
After all, it was deserted.
Now, why don't you all come in
and make yourselves at home?
The mansion's western-style, so
feel free to keep your shoes on.
[MIKURU]
Wow, what a lovely room!
It's nice we each get
to have our own room
instead of having to share.
By the way, the doors
do have locks, right?
Of course. And they're
not automatic locks,
so you won't get
stuck in the hall.
However, I would appreciate it
if you didn't lose your keys.
If you want, you can
stay with me in my room.
Only if you behave,
you got that?
Okay...
It's suspicious because
nothing looks suspicious.
And if it looks suspicious
to begin with, well, then what?
[HARUHI] It'd be suspicious,
of course! Geez...
[KYON] In other words,
to her, everything,
including things that aren't
suspicious, are suspicious.
[HARUHI]
I got it!
[KYON]
Got what?
The culprit!
What culprit? What're
you talking about?
Look, nothing's
even happened yet.
We just got here, okay?
[HARUHI] My gut says it's
the owner of this house!
Keiichi did it! And the
first victim will be...
...Mikuru!
[KYON] Would you stop
saying stuff like that?
We're their guests!
Can't you just act like a
normal high school student?!
I guess you're right.
Maybe we should go swimming.
We got the whole ocean
to ourselves down there,
so we might as well take
advantage of it, right?
[KYON]
Oh, man...
Although, I'm sure Haruhi
would never seriously wish
for anyone to die, it's scary
to hear her go off like that.
[KYON] This moment is the best
part about this whole trip.
Now this is what having a
retreat by the sea's all about.
Hm?
[KOIZUMI] You know, we all have
different ideas of what's fun.
A person should spend
their time on vacation
doing the things they like.
That's especially true
for Miss Suzumiya.
We need to keep her occupied
so that she doesn't get bored.
And we wouldn't want that
to happen, now, would we?
Kyon, Koizumi! Come on,
stop sittin' around
and get over here!
Heh, heh! I'm coming, too!
Over here! Over here!
[KYON]
Too many beach balls!
[giggles]
Huh?
[cheering]
[ALL sighing]
[KYON'S LITTLE SISTER]
That was so much fun today.
Wow, this is so delicious!
Who made all this?
I'm glad you like it.
The butler, Arakawa,
is also the head
chef around here.
I'd like to
personally thank him.
Please call him in
when he's done.
[KYON'S LITTLE SISTER]
Can I have some of that?
Wow, she sure eats a lot.
[MORI] Would you like
something to drink?
[MIKURU]
What's wrong?
[KYON'S LITTLE SISTER]
I don't like bell peppers...
If you wanna grow up
to be like Miss Asahina,
then you're gonna
have to eat them.
[KYON] It's not often
we get to eat this good.
[chuckles]
Wow! I can't believe
this is free!
I just wish the school cafeteria
had a spread like this!
It'd be like heaven!
[ALL laughing]
[KYON screams]
--[HARUHI cackles]
--[KYON] So after living it up,
courtesy of Mr.
Tamaru's hospitality,
we were able to get
through the first day
without anything terribly
strange happening.
Now, if the story ended there,
it would've been perfect.
No such luck, though...
[KYON]
The next morning, as if on cue,
a huge storm rolled in.
The master's not what
you'd call a morning person,
and he tends to be...
difficult when he wakes up.
Please excuse his absence
at the table in the mornings,
and I do appreciate your
understanding in the matter.
Great, that's just our luck.
A typhoon hits as we're
starting our vacation.
[KOIZUMI] The storm seems
to be moving fairly quickly.
Things'll be back to normal
in a couple days.
You'll see. It'll disappear
as quickly as it appeared.
[KYON] It's strange, though. I
don't remember hearing anything
about a typhoon yesterday.
[KYON] Who's head did
this massive storm
come creeping out of?
Okay, what we've got here
is a deserted island
in the middle of a storm.
This is a rare opportunity.
We might even experience
something weird.
Awesome...
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON] Taking the boats out
that day was not an option.
The waves were just too big.
Now, thanks to Haruhi's wish,
we found ourselves the
unwilling guests trapped
on a spooky deserted island.
A closed circle...? No way...
[KYON]
Since we couldn't go outside,
we decided to spend the day
in the game room which was
in the mansion's basement.
Here's my Super Ultra
Miracle Eccentric Serve!
[KYON'S LITTLE SISTER]
Hey, whatcha readin'?
Is it good? Huh?
[KYON growls]
I call... Reach!
Wrong! My hand's
wroth 10,000 points.
That is definitely a
full hand, Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON] Good we're not
playing for money.
I'm glad to see you're all
having a good time here.
If you guys don't mind,
can I sit in for a hand?
Please.
What's it mean when
you pitch in a piece?
Please excuse me, everybody.
I'm afraid I have some work
that needs to get done.
Enjoy yourselves.
Keiichi and Yutaka Tamaru.
Mr. Arakawa and Ms. Mori.
They seem normal
even though they're
acquaintances of Koizumi's.
We'll meet a couple
more characters
before something
strange can happen.
I call Reach!
[ALL]
Who is the king?
I am the king!
Okay, number 2! You have to
turn around, look back at us,
and say, "I love you!"
Who has number 2?
I love you.
[growls] No, not
like that, Yuki!
You have to say it with
more feeling, all right?!
I love you.
Go on, Kyon.
Show her how to do it.
Why do I have to?
It doesn't matter why.
It's the king's orders, okay?!
--I love--
--[HARUHI] Psyche!
[KYON]
Selfish king...
That's typical Haruhi for you.
I thought I'd be able
to skip the rest of this
chapter of adolescence,
with little more than a laugh.
But that's not how
the dealer cut the deck.
Now, I don't know
who this "dealer" is,
or what kind of deck they
were cutting for that matter,
but if I knew who
this dealer was,
I'd make sure they'd never
shuffle cards or cut a deck
for the rest of the year.
Hey, Haruhi-- Ah!
[KYON grunts]
What a wimp!
You should expect pillow fights
when you're on a retreat!
[KYON] Where does that
girl get her energy?
She was up all night.
[KOIZUMI]
Pillow fights, huh?
No wonder Miss Suzumiya was
going through all the rooms.
It looks like she went around
and confiscated all the pillows
on the second floor.
[KYON] She's stealing all of the
weapons before the battle, huh?
Mr. Arakawa, is there
anything wrong?
I sent Mori up to Mr. Yutaka's
room a while ago.
When she came back down, she
told me that he wasn't there.
He isn't in the house?
His bed hadn't been slept in,
and we looked for him
in the usual places, but I'm
afraid he's nowhere to be found.
Have you gone in Mr. Keiichi's
room and checked with him?
[ARAKAWA] Yes. Well, we
tried calling the phone in
the master's bedroom,
but there was no answer.
[HARUHI] What's that? Did you
say that Mr. Yutaka's missing
and Mr. Keiichi isn't
answering his phone?
If asked to summarize, yes,
that is exactly what I said.
[KOIZUMI] We should probably
check Mr. Keiichi's room.
Mr. Arakawa, do you have a key?
The master's chambers are
different from the other rooms.
Unfortunately, he's the only
one with the keys to it.
It's a precaution. He brings
work-related documents
to the island.
[KOIZUMI] We'd better go up
to his room and try knocking.
Come on, Kyon. I've got
a bad feeling about this.
Yuki, Mikuru, let's go, guys.
Stay here, Little Sister,
we'll be right back.
[HARUHI]
Huh...?
Huh?
[KOIZUMI]
Mr. Keiichi! Mr. Keiichi!
If you're here, answer us!
No good, it's locked.
I don't think we have a choice.
We're going to have to
break the door down
to get in this room.
We can't waste any more time
talking, he might be in trouble.
All right.
Very good, sir.
[grunting]
[KYON]
Breaking doors like this only
happens in the movies, right?
[yelling]
[groans]
[gasps]
[KYON] Impossible...
You're joking, right...?