[chattering]
[KYON] The arts festival and
its chaotic aftermath were over.
The mountains winds are
beginning to whip up,
and you can just hear
the footsteps of winter
drawing ever closer.
December is almost upon us.
Now this old building,
also known as
the club room wing,
has been here since
the school was built.
And thanks in part
to its thin walls,
even though we were inside,
you could still feel the chill
right down to your bones.
[gasps]
[KYON]
The SOS Brigade always seems
to get involved
with strange things.
Well, actually, I'm the one
getting involved
with strange things.
But even so, it's
not something weird
has to happen to us
on a daily basis.
Besides, if life dropped a
crazy bomb on me every day,
my body wouldn't take it.
And it'd just crumble.
It would be even
worse for my mood.
[sighs]
[KYON] Still, when Haruhi isn't
around, it's really quiet.
It's kinda nice.
[KYON] Then again,
maybe it's a bit too quiet.
[KYON]
Come to think of it,
it's been six months since
I first met Haruhi,
Miss Asahina, and the others.
[KYON] We've been
through a lot together.
And sure, Haruhi's
provoked a lot of it,
but not necessarily all of it.
Well, either way,
one thing's for sure.
It was always at times like this
when we were just
kicking back and relaxing
that Haruhi would
bust through that door--
Everyone! Listen up!
I've got some really good news!
[KYON]
What? Again?
Whenever Haruhi describes
something as being "good,"
news or otherwise, rarely has
that ever been the case.
And that's especially true
for Miss Asahina and myself.
What is it this time?
I've got everything all
set up to get us a heater
for this ice box of a room.
Oh! Your tea!
You know that appliance store
that sponsored our movie?
Well, I just got the owner
to give us a heater for free!
He called me up and said
he had an extra heater
he wanted to get rid of!
It's a model from last year,
and it's been sitting
in storage so long,
they forgot they had it!
[KYON]
I just can't believe
there's an appliance
store owner out there
who's both willing
and kind enough
to call Haruhi and
offer her anything.
I'm sure she must've forced
the deal on him somehow.
Okay, Kyon! I want you
to go to the store
and pick it up for us right now.
Right now? Like now-now?
Right. You, now, right now.
[KYON]
Lemme get this straight:
You want me to go
down the mountain,
the one I have to climb up
and down every morning.
You want me to go down
that thing right now
to an appliance store that is
two whole train stations away,
pick up a heater, and then
lug that thing back here?
That's right!
'Cause if you don't, the guy
might change his mind,
and then we're
out a free heater!
Don't complain,
just hurry up and go!
You're bored anyway, aren't ya?!
[KYON]
Oh, that's great.
Sitting in this room was enough
to label you as
being bored, nice.
Aren't you bored?
Why don't you do it?
I can't!
There's something important I
need to take care of right now.
[laughs]
[MIKURU]
Hm?
[HARUHI]
Koizumi is the deputy chief,
and you're just a
rank and file member.
That's the deal in
every group I know of.
The grunts always
work their butts off.
Naturally, the SOS Brigade
totally supports that policy.
[KYON]
Oh, well...
For once, Haruhi's made
a reasonable request.
I give up.
[KOIZUMI]
Please do be careful out there.
[KYON]
Besides, I was just thinking
how this place could
use a heater anyway.
[KYON] If she's going to force
Miss Asahina or Nagato to go,
then I'll go.
[MIKURU]
Oh...
Hold on!
[KYON gasps]
I heard it's going
to be chilly today!
Thank you.
Hurry up and go!
--Go on, get going!
--[MIKURU gasps]
[KYON sighs]
[HARUHI] Well, now that
he's outta the way,
[MIKURU]
Huh?
[HARUHI] Mikuru, I wanna take
a couple of pictures of you.
Do you mind posing?
[MIKURU] Huh?! What are
the pictures gonna be for?
It's for the DVD!
I'm gonna make a DVD of "The
Adventures of Mikuru Asahina."
And I still need to
shoot a sexy cover for it.
Wha... You mean you're really
going to go through with that?
B-But I thought you said
you weren't going to.
[HARUHI] I just said that 'cause
Kyon was naggin' me about it.
But now that I got rid of him,
nothing's gonna stop me.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KOIZUMI sighs]
[KYON] The first day
I had to climb this hill
to get to school, I hated it.
But after walking up
and down the thing
for the last six months,
I've gotten used to it.
I've gotten used to A.,
hiking to and from school,
and B., the SOS Brigade.
Funny how that works.
[KYON]
Hm...
I wonder what Haruhi's
doing right now,
since I'm not around.
I just hope she's not bored
and treating Miss Asahina
like some kind of
toy or something.
[HARUHI] Koizumi!
Hold the bounce card for me.
[KOIZUMI]
Right, got it.
[HARUHI]
Mikuru, stop spacing out! Pose!
Come on, pose! Pose!
[MIKURU]
Uh... O-Okay...
[HARUHI] Come on, smile like
you're flirting with a cute guy.
More seductive! Come on!
That's not gonna cut
it for the male fans.
Get sultry, girl!
[HARUHI]
Cool! Costume change!
Put this one on!
Come on, stop stalling!
[MIKURU whimpering]
[HARUHI, MIKURU grunting]
[HARUHI]
Mikuru! Come on! Let's go!
[MIKURU]
No! I can do it myself!
[HARUHI]
Like I haven't seen it before!
Here, it's faster if I help!
[MIKURU screams]
[MIKURU]
No, not my bra, too!
[HARUHI] Well, you're gonna
have to take it off anyway.
Mikuru! Wow, those things
are even bigger!
You look dynamite, girl!
[MIKURU]
It's cold!
[MIKURU whimpering]
[HARUHI]
Hold still!
--[MIKURU screams]
--Oh! That's not good.
--My tea's gone cold.
[coins clinking]
[machine beeps]
[MIKURU]
Ohh... It's really cold in here!
Could we stop now?
This is so embarrassing!
Mikuru... You need to have
a little more
confidence in yourself.
You're the best
mascot on campus!
I wouldn't have picked you if
you didn't have what it takes!
Right, Koizumi?
[KOIZUMI]
It's exactly as you say.
[HARUHI]
Okay, next! Try this!
Huh? Again?
--[HARUHI grunts]
--[MIKURU screams] No!
[MIKURU]
I can do that myself!
[MIKURU yelps]
[HARUHI]
Hurry up!
We have to finish
shooting this stuff today!
Come on!
[MIKURU whimpering]
[HARUHI sighs]
[KYON sniffles]
[HARUHI]
Put this one on next!
[MIKURU] But this nurse
outfit and that one...
Um... I don't really remember
wearing either one
of them in the movie.
Are these pictures we're taking
really for the cover of the DVD?
[HARUHI]
Yeah! Of course they are!
But I just came up
with another idea!
With all these photos,
we can publish a picture book!
What do you think
about that, Koizumi?
[KOIZUMI]
I think it's a great idea.
[MIKURU]
Uh...
No! Wait!
The DVD needs a bonus
features section!
We could put these
pictures there!
What do you think about
that idea, Koizumi?
[KOIZUMI]
I think it's a fantastic idea.
[MIKURU cries]
[MIKURU whimpers]
[HARUHI]
Stick your arm in there!
Looks like we might be in for
a little bit of
rain today, doesn't it?
[HARUHI]
Nice!
It's the funniest thing ever.
You're kidding!
Well, no, not really.
[GIRLS laugh]
[HARUHI]
Heh, heh, good! Next outfit!
What?! We've got more outfits?
[HARUHI]
Just gotta find the zipper...
[MIKURU whimpering]
[HARUHI laughs]
[MIKURU screams]
[MIKURU]
No! I-I need that!
[HARUHI] I want a shot of you
flashing some panty at us!
So these have to go! And soon!
Ha, ha! This is so fun!
Taking all your clothes off!
[MIKURU screams]
Well, there's the
heater I promised her.
Can you carry it back okay?
Oh, yeah. I think I can manage.
And about the girls,
how are those three cutie
pies doin' these days?
Pretty good. The energetic one's
starting to get on my nerves.
The commercial
help business any?
Honestly, I haven't seen
any difference so far.
[KYON]
Figures.
Putting a commercial
in the middle of a movie
showing at a high
school arts festival
isn't what you'd call a
stroke of marketing genius.
I'm surprised this guy
actually sponsored it.
That reminds me.
When the energetic
one called today,
she mentioned something
about a sequel.
Is it true? Are you really
going to make another movie?
Well, if she says we're
making another movie,
we're making another movie.
She asked if I'd
want to sponsor it,
and I told her I'd be
happy to, so... [laughs]
So I guess you can consider
this heater my donation
to your next cinematic wonder.
[KYON]
So that's how she got it.
Guess I'll head back now.
Thank you very much
for the heater.
No worries, take care!
[STUDENTS]
Ameobas are red, a-i-u-e-o!
Little shrimp in floating moss,
swimming to and fro!
Persimmon tree, chestnut tree,
ka-ki-ku-ke-ko!
A woodpecker pecking at
a dead zelkova tree just so!
Pour some vinegar on cowpeas,
sa-shi-su-se-so!
I stabbed a fish in a stream
that was very, very shallow!
We all stand up when the trumpet
blows, ta-chi-tsu-te-to!
[TEACHER] When we stood,
it flew off with a...
[STUDENTS]
Konk-konk-konk-konk-boom!
A slow crawls very slow,
na-ni-nu-ne-no!
[TEACHER]
Na-ni-nu-ne-no!
[STUDENT A]
Aha! So you are the culprit!
[STUDENT B] Oh, the red
player has picked number 14!
Very well, I wonder how that's
going to affect the game today!
Next question!
[STUDENT C]
Amazing! Just by showing up,
she's changed the
atmosphere on the stage!
But she seems completely
different, doesn't she?
She's not the same as
she was a few minutes ago!
What a terrifying little girl!
[STUDENT D]
Tanmen noodle set!
Fried rice set!
Tempura and cold soba set!
[STUDENT E]
Young man, ace!
Middle aged, ace!
Retirement, ace!
Non-promoted, ace!
Next year, ace!
Unfortunate, ace!
I love it after all, ace!
[STUDENT F] Why don't you
do your best to beat me?!
Bring it on!
What you guys have done
is snappy, crackly,
and totally obvious to us!
He looks like a child!
But he's pretty
subtle on the inside.
A powerful ally all over town!
[STUDENT G]
Now, now, now, now!
Can you not see this
crest that I hold?
[STUDENT H] Because...
I... am ze queen of France!
[STUDENT I]
Now that hit a weird spot!
[STUDENT J]
You've still got a way's to go!
[Student H singing]
[STUDENT K] Hello! We're
the Arctic Sea ice candies!
[STUDENT L]
Bang.
[STUDENT K] You know, Yuki,
you're as sexy as ever!
[STUDENT L]
Where are you lookin', pervert?
I'm callin' the cops.
[STUDENT K]
Starting with a low blow?
I feel like I've been accused of
groping people on
a crammed train.
[STUDENT L] Yeah.
By the way, it's winter now.
[STUDENT K]
Right, it's winter.
And speaking of winter--
[STUDENT L]
Baseball's off season.
[STUDENT K]
Cool point there, Yuki.
Why, even the WBC is
shaking in their cleats!
[STUDENT L]
I'm really looking forward to
seeing who gets the pink slip.
[STUDENT K] That's a really
dark way of enjoying it.
But okay!
Well, you know! It's almost
Christmas, isn't it?
[STUDENT L]
I wanna eat a hot pot.
[STUDENT K]
Right!
You can't do without
hot pots in winter!
[STUDENT L]
What do you put in your hot pot?
[STUDENT K]
Let's see!
Nappa cabbage, chicken,
pork, leeks, natto, tofu!
Well, what about you, Yuki?
[STUDENT L]
Brown bear.
[STUDENT K]
Wow, Yuki! You're a hunter?
Even Masaki would
cry and run away!
[STUDENT L] Yeah, but I think
about how the bear feels.
I feel sorry for it
and lose my appetite.
[STUDENT K] Then don't
put it into your hot pot
to begin with, woman!
[STUDENT L] I'll play
the part of the brown bear.
[STUDENT K]
What? You will?
[STUDENT L]
And you play the pot.
[STUDENT K]
Here it comes, folks!
The worst comedy
skit in history!
Get ready!
[TANIGUCHI]
Hey, Kyon!
What are you lurkin'
around down here for?
It's obvious, isn't it?
I'm carrying stuff around.
Hah! You sure are a hard worker!
You're running errands
for Suzumiya, aren't you?
[KYON] I guess six months was
all it took for my classmates to
fully comprehend the situation
I've gotten myself into.
Are you takin' that
thing back to school?
Oh, wow! You're a hard worker!
You're telling me.
--Well, see ya.
--Yeah.
See ya tomorrow!
[KYON]
Mm.
Damn!
Now it's gonna start raining!
[KYON]
The weather forecast said
there was only a 10%
chance of rain today.
Yet another thing
that can't be trusted.
I hope it doesn't
turn into a downpour.
[KOIZUMI]
Oh.
Looks like it started raining.
[MIKURU]
I wonder if Kyon's all right.
[KYON] I've never wanted to be
in that room more than I do now.
First thing I'm gonna
do is grab myself
a cup of Miss Asahina's
tea and warm up my body.
Along with my heart.
[TSURUYA]
Yoo-hoo!
Hey, is Mikuru here?
Nagato? Are you
the only one here?
I wanna see if she'll
trade cleaning duties
with me tomorrow.
So I came to ask her.
Do you know where she is?
Oh, she's over there, huh?
Cool, thanks!
[KYON grunts]
[STUDENT M]
To the left!
[STUDENTS] Right, left,
right, left, right, left!
[STUDENT M]
To the right!
[STUDENTS] Right, left,
right, left, right, left!
[STUDENT M]
Stand in place!
[STUDENTS] Right, left,
right, left, right, left!
[STUDENT M]
Side to side!
[STUDENTS] Right, left,
right, left, right, left!
[KYON grunts]
[sighs]
Oh, brother.
[footsteps]
Hey, Kyon! Were you out
running errands again?
Miss Tsuruya!
That's why!
Huh? What do you mean?
[TSURUYA giggles]
Nope, nothing at all!
You hard worker!
Hm... You're soaked to the bone.
Here!
--Thank you.
--Well, see ya!
Just give my
handkerchief to Mikuru
when you return her scarf.
[TSURUYA laughs]
[KYON]
I don't think I'll ever get
what's going on
in that girl's head.
She's a nice person
though, I'll say that.
[KYON grunts]
[KYON]
Oh, Nagato.
You're the only one here?
[KYON grunts]
So, where's Haruhi
and the others?
[MIKURU yelps]
[HARUHI]
Yeah! Now that's how
you're supposed
to land on your butt!
We got it! Moving on!
[MIKURU]
Uh...
[whimpers]
Ouchie!
--[cries]
--[HARUHI laughs]
[HARUHI] I'm in awe
of your clumsiness.
Are you doing this on purpose?
Koizumi! Take over for me.
This is how ya do it, like this.
[KYON]
I'm a little worried about
where the three of them are
and what they're
doing right now.
But schlepping that rotten
heater up that hill
really wore me out.
The worst part is,
I'm gonna have to
go right back down that hill
again when I go home!
How messed up is that?
[KYON]
Come on... Come on, come on.
Man! My hands are so cold.
[sighs]
I'm just so tired...
[snoring]
[HARUHI gasps]
Oh, Haruhi, it's only you.
Yeah, so?
Is that a problem?
No, I don't have
a problem with it.
You didn't go and
draw something silly
on my face this time, did you?
Of course not! I'm not
a little kid, Kyon!
Hey, where's everybody else?
[HARUHI] It didn't look
like you were gonna wake up
any time soon,
so they all went home.
But... you coulda
just gone home.
Why'd you stay behind?
I couldn't really help it!
You were still sleeping.
Whaddya want me to do?
I gotta lock the door
before I leave.
Besides, it's still
raining out there!
[KYON]
Uh.
[HARUHI]
Okay, hand it over.
Huh?
My cardigan!
[KYON]
Uh... Oh.
[KYON] Okay... So that
one belongs to Haruhi.
But... who does this
other sweater belong to?
[KYON] Whoa, that means
that Miss Asahina was
changing clothes right next
to me while I was sleeping!
Dammit! Why did I
have to fall asleep?!
If I pretended to be asleep,
I could've seen--
Well? Everyone left
school a while ago.
Come on, let's get outta here.
Okay.
I'm kinda stuck though.
I didn't bring an
umbrella with me today.
[HARUHI] One'll be
enough for the two of us.
[HARUHI]
Aim that thing over here more.
I'm getting all wet.
But you've got a ton
of umbrella over there.
Uh! Oh, nice one.
This isn't even yours.
This thing's got "faculty"
stenciled on it.
[HARUHI]
It belongs to the school,
so there shouldn't be
anything wrong with
a couple of students
using it, right?
What? You wanna go
home all sopping wet?
Fine! Then I won't
let you use it!
[HARUHI laughs]
[KYON] Geez... I went
to all that trouble
bringing the heater back,
and little miss brigade
leader over there
can't even say, "Thank you."
Typical Haruhi.
Hey, wait up!
[laughs]
Unn!