[KYON]
Okay.
Asking somebody how long they've
believed in Santa Claus
is so stupid,
you can't even consider it
a topic suitable for
idle conversation.
But if you still
wanna know how long
I've believe in some old, fat
guy who wears a funky red suit,
I can tell you this:
I've never believed
in him... ever.
The Santa that showed up at my
kindergarten Christmas festival?
I knew he was fake.
And I never saw Mommy
kissing Santa or anything.
But I have to say that
even as a little kid,
I knew better than to
believe in some old man
that only worked one day a year.
Now, having said that,
it wasn't until I got older
that I realized aliens, time
travelers, ghosts, monsters,
ESPers, evil syndicates,
and the anime slash manga
slash fantasy-flick heroes
that fight said evil
syndicates... were also fake.
Okay, I guess I always knew
those things were bogus,
I just didn't want to admit it.
All I ever wanted was for an
alien, time traveler, ghost,
monster, ESPer, evil syndicate
or the hero who fought 'em
to just appear and say, "Hey."
Unfortunately, reality
is a hard road indeed.
Yep, you gotta admit,
the laws of physics
definitely puts
a damper on things.
I even stopped
watching those TV shows
about aliens and
ghosts and stuff.
Aliens, time travelers, ESPers,
'course they don't exist.
But a little part of me
wishes that they did.
I guess I've grown up
and realized
that I can think
about those things
and still accept reality.
[KYON] But by the time
I got out of junior high,
I pretty much outgrew
that kinda stuff.
And I guess I got
used to the idea of
living in an ordinary world.
And just like that--
I was in high school.
And that's when I met her...
I'm Haruhi Suzumiya
from East Junior High.
First off, I'm not interested
in ordinary people.
But if any of you are aliens,
time travelers, or ESPers,
please come see me. That is all.
[KYON]
Is that supposed to be funny?
[KYON] There stood before me
this amazing, beautiful girl.
Uh...
[gasping]
O-kay... Next?
[KYON] I bet everyone
thought she was kidding,
but it wasn't a joke.
And it wasn't anything
to laugh about.
Haruhi is always dead serious.
And that's how we first met.
Looking back, I wanna believe
that it was just a coincidence.
[KYON] As long as Haruhi
Suzumiya is sitting quietly,
she's just like any other
extremely beautiful
high school girl.
And my seat just happens
to be in front of her.
I mean, can you
blame me for wanting
to exploit this seating
arrangement so I could, um...
get to know her better?
Hey, that stuff you were
saying when you were
introducing yourself,
were you serious about all that?
What about the stuff
I was saying?
[KYON] Well, you know,
about aliens and stuff.
Why? Are you an alien
or something?
[KYON]
Well, no, but I just--
Well, no, but you just what?
Well, I-- Just forget it.
Then why are we even
talking right now?
You're wasting my time. Ugh.
[KYON]
Hmm?
[chuckling]
[KYON]
Later on,
I found out that quite
a few of my new classmates
were from the same
junior high as Haruhi.
[TANIGUCHI] Look, if you've
got the hots for her,
take my advice:
Forget it.
After being in the same class
as her for three years,
I know her pretty well.
Let's just say she's what you
might call beyond eccentric.
Like her introduction?
Yep! In junior high,
I can't remember a day
when she wasn't doing
something completely wacky.
You ever hear the quad
scribbles incident?
No, what's that?
You know that thing that draws
lines on the athletic field?
Agh, what d'ya call
that thing again?
Whatever. Well, she used
that thing to draw
this big, mysterious symbol
on the school quad.
She snuck into the school
grounds at night to draw it.
Yeah, I remember
reading about that.
I think it was in the local
section of the daily newspaper.
It sorta looked like
a botched version
of a Nazca drawing, didn't it?
[KYON] So, you're telling me
she did this all by herself?
[TANIGUCHI] No doubt. And she
totally admitted doing it.
Oh yeah, and then one morning,
I get to class early.
All the desks were
shoved out into the hall!
Then there's the time she
painted a star on the roof.
And this other time when she
plastered these talismans...
[KYON]
What the hell's she doing...?
[TANIGUCHI]
You know,
like the ones you use
to reanimate corpses?
I have no idea why.
But all the same, man, she's
pretty popular with the guys.
She's not too hard
to look at, you know?
And she's freakin'
good at sports.
And, on top of that,
she gets good grades.
She's a super weirdo.
But if she's standing there
quietly, you'd never know.
[KUNIKIDA] Somethin' tells me
you have more to say about her.
[TANIGUCHI]
For a while,
she was goin' out with
one joker after another.
I think the longest any one
guy lasted was about a week.
And the guy that had the
shortest relationship with her?
He asked her out,
she said okay,
and it ended five minutes later.
I don't have any time to deal
with ordinary humans!
[TANIGUCHI] Then why the hell'd
you say okay?
Hmm?
I mean, that's what
I heard, really!
I don't know why, but she
never turns a guy down
when he steps up to ask her out.
And so, before you get any
bright ideas, buddy,
take my advice:
forget it.
[KYON]
Forget it? What's to forget
when I haven't even
though about it?
[TANIGUCHI] If you were me,
there's only one girl
in this class to go after.
And that's her.
[TANIGUCHI] Ryoko Asakura.
And I'm telling ya,
she's in the top 3 on the
freshman hottie list.
So what, are you telling us that
you've already checked out
all the freshman girls?
Heck yeah! I ranked
'em all from A to D
and I even went so far as
to memorize the full names
of all the A-list girls, buddy.
Really? So what ranking
did Asakura get?
She gets Double-A plus!
On top of being gorgeous, I bet
her personality is wonderful.
[panting]
[BOYS murmuring]
[KYON]
Now, all this was happening
when Haruhi Suzumiya was
still acting sorta normal.
For that whole month, even
I was feeling pretty good.
However, it should be noted
that bits and pieces
of Haruhi eccentricites
were already starting
to make themselves known.
Haruhi Eccentricity number 1:
A different hairstyle everyday.
Monday.
Tuesday.
Wednesday.
Thursday.
Friday.
As the days passed,
the number of places
she'd tie off her
hair increased.
On Monday, she resets her hair,
and then adds off a tie-off
point each day until Friday.
Wonder what her hair
looks like on Sunday.
Think I'd like to see that.
[KYON]
Haruhi Eccentricity number 2:
Our PE classe is seperated
into boys and girls.
When changing into uniforms,
girls use the odd
numbered classrooms
and boys used the even numbers.
It didn't matter that guys
were standing around,
she'd just start changing
out of her school uniform.
[STUDENTS screaming]
[KYON]
To Haruhi, guys were pretty much
the same as a bag of potatoes.
[KYON] Eccentricity number 3:
It was rather irritating
that Haruhi joined
every team in
every extra-curricular club
the school had to offer.
Every single one of
the sports clubs lobbied
for her to join their
respective teams,
and she'd turned
every one of 'em down.
She'd change clubs on a daily
basis depending on her mood.
In the end though,
she didn't remain a member
of a single one of the clubs.
I mean, what the hell does
she wanna do anyway?
[KYON] And before I knew it,
it was the day after
the Golden Week vacation.
[TANIGUCHI]
Kyon! What's up?
Hey.
[KYON] And by the way, Kyon?
That's my nickname.
And I really wish people would
stop calling me that already.
[KYON] Oh. I guess today's
Wednesday, isn't it?
And with that thought, something
must've snapped inside me.
I can't think of
any reason why...
So, do you cahnge
your hairstyle everyday
to ward off alien invaders?
[KYON] I was talking
to Haruhi Suzumiya.
So when did you notice?
[KYON]
Mmm... A while ago.
Oh, I see.
Actually, I have this theory
that each day of the week
has its own image
with a specific color
that only goes with that day.
And by colors, I'd say...
[KYON] It felt almost
like we were having a
real conversation
for the first time.
...and Thursday's green.
Friday is gold,
and Saturday is brown. And
the color for Sunday is white.
[KYON] Hey, I kinda understand
what she's talking about.
[KYON] So, if you
turn that into numbers,
Monday'd be zero, and
Sunday'd be six, right?
Right.
[KYON] I kinda feel that
Monday's more like a one.
I don't think anybody was
asking for your opinion.
[KYON]
Oh, is that so?
Hm.
Have I met you somewhere before?
Like, maybe in the past,
or something like that?
Not likely.
[exhales]
[KYON] Usually, an event
is triggered by something
that's considered trivial.
Well, this must've
been my trigger.
I was surprised that
Haruhi even replied
with a half-decent answer.
I totally thought she'd
say something like,
"
I mean, you get the picture...
[KYON] And so, when Haruhi
came to class the next day
with her long hair
all chopped off,
I was rather disturbed by it.
I mean, cutting
it short like that
the day after I
made my comment...
It's a little rash,
don't you think?
Not really.
[KYON]
Ever since that day,
talking to Haruhi right
before homeroom started
was becoming sort of a ritual.
[KYON] Is it true you've dumped
every guy you've ever dated?
And just what
gives you the right
to ask me a question like that?
I don't know about
anything you've heard.
Whatever. You wanna believe it?
It's probably true.
Well, with all that dating,
wasn't there at least one guy
you were even a
little serious about?
Absolutely not.
They all took themselves
way too seriously,
and not even one of those dorks
was an alien, time traveler,
or even an ESPer.
[KYON]
That's how people are normally.
Okay, so what's
with most of them
asking me out over the phone?
I mean, shouldn't important
stuff like that
be done face-to-face,
not phone-to-phone?
Yeah, I mean, if it were me...
[KYON] I'll just agree
with her for now.
Yeah, well, none of that's
important anyway!
[KYON]
So what is?
Here's the problem:
So far, the way it looks
is that all the men
in this entire universe
are pathetic.
I mean, all through
junior high,
that was the one thing that
irritated me the most.
All right then,
so what kind of guy
would you have really have been
into? An alien or something?
[HARUHI]
Yeah! Anything like an alien
or something else
along those lines.
Anyway, as long as the person
isn't an ordinary human,
I don't care if it's
a boy or a girl.
Hang on a sec,
what's wrong with being human?
I mean, why do they
have to be an alien?
Because that way,
life's more interesting.
[school bell chimes]
[KYON sighs]
Hey, Kyon!
You need to tell me what kind
of magic spell you're using.
[KYON]
What're you talking about?
I have never seen Suzumiya
talk that long before,
and I'm not exaggerating, man!
What the hell'd you say to her?
[KYON]
Huh...
Wonder what I could've
said to her.
I think it was all
pretty random stuff.
This is a phenomenon.
Kyon's always gone after
the strange ones;
the weirder the better.
Little louder, please,
so everyone can hear you.
[ASAKURA]
I wanna know how you did it.
No matter how much
I've tried to talk to her,
I can't get Haruhi to answer
any of my questions.
What do you do to
get her to open up?
Do you have any tips for me?
No idea.
[ASAKURA] Hmm... Still,
I think it's a good thing.
I've been sorta worried
about her always being
completely alone in our class.
I think it's really great she's
made at least one friend here.
A friend, huh?
Well, just keep doing
whatever you're doing,
cause maybe she'll warm
up to the rest of us.
I mean, since we're all
in the same class,
it'd be really for the best
if everyone got a long,
and that's why
I'm counting on you.
[KYON]
Easy for you to say.
In fact, from now on,
if there's anything we
need to say to her,
we'll just talk to you,
and you can tell her for us.
[growls]
Hey, hang on a sec!
What do ya think I am;
am I supposed to be your
spokesperson or something?!
Pretty please?
[giggling]
[gasps]
Kyon, we're buddies, aren't we?
We're pals, right?
[KYON]
Everyone's turned into an idiot.
Apparently we're changing seats.
I picked a number out of a
cookie tin that gave me the seat
next to the window
second from the back.
An awesome seat if I may say so.
Farewell, Haruhi. Forever.
Coincidence?
[KYON] Hey, I heard you checked
out all the clubs at school.
Give me a heads up
if you know about
any interesting ones, okay?
Absolutely none.
[KYON]
An instant reply.
Absolutely none!
[KYON] It seems she likes to use
the word "absolutely" a lot.
I thought things would
get a little better
when I got into highschool,
but it's the same here
as it's been throughout all
these mandatory school years.
Maybe I'm just in
the wrong school.
[KYON] I sorta wonder
what her criteria are.
There was a club called the
"Mystery Research Club."
[KYON]
Yeah? How was that?
It was hilarious.
They told me they've never
had anything they could
even remotely call a case.
And the members were a bunch
of mystery novel otakus.
Definitely not
master detectives.
[KYON]
Well, that figures.
Yeah, well I had high hopes for
the Supernatural Phenomenon
Research Club, too,
but that thing was just
a bunch of occult freaks.
What do you think of it?
I don't think about it.
Oh man! I'm so bored!
With all these clubs, you'd
think they're be a couple of
really strange cool
ones out there.
Listen, you can't help
it if there aren't any.
Besides, us normal human types,
we gotta be happy
with what we're given, you know
what I'm saying?
You could look at it this way:
the people who don't like what
they got are the same people
who invent things
and make discoveries
and advance civilization.
They made airplanes 'cause
they wanted to fly,
and they made cars and trains
'cause they wanted to go
from place to place.
It's as simple as that.
The only reason that we've got
all the things we have now
is because a certain group
of people got together
and used their talent
or imagination
or genius or whatever
to make it all possible.
Ordinary people are
probably better off
living their ordinary,
little lives
in an ordinary manner.
Shut up.
[KYON]
Hmm?
[growls]
[KYON]
Perhaps it was this conversation
that sparked the idea...
[KYON]
It happened suddenly.
[grunts]
[whimpers]
What's wrong with you?!
I got an idea!
About what?
I can't believe I didn't
realize it before!
It's so obvious!
What is?
If it doesn't exist,
I should just make it myself!
Make what yourself?
Make a club!
[sighs]
I hear ya, but you gotta
calm down, all right?
What's with you?! This is
what we're talkin' about!
You should be happy you're
about this development.
Well... we're in the
middle of class.
[chuckles nervously]
Hmm?
[school bell chimes]
You're gonna help.
[KYON] I feel like I'm being
bullied outta my lunch money.
What d'ya need help with?
Starting my new club,
that's what!
First, tell me why I'm the
one who's gotta help you
set up a club that's your
idea in the first place.
And you can let go
of the tie, now.
I'll find us a room
and some members,
and I want you to personally
handle all the paperwork...
[KYON]
She's not listening.
Why don't you tell me what
kind of club it's gonna be.
[HARUHI]
Who cares about that right now?!
We've gotta go
make the club first!
You got it? Do all that stuff
before school ends today.
I'll find a room for
the club by then!
Okie-dokie?
[KYON] Rules for the creation of
a new extra-curricular group...
At least five members,
a teacher to supervise,
a name, the name of
the person in charge,
the purpose of the organization.
There's nothing for me to do.
It's all in the back of
the student handbook.
And I can bet money on this:
Haruhi's little scheme?
Nothing about it's gonna
contribute to making school life
more creative or more fun.
Of that I'm positive.
This is going to be
our new clubroom!
[KYON] Hang on, I don't even
know where we are right now.
This is the cultural department!
The art club's got the art room,
and the wind ensemble has got
the music room, am I right?
Club's that don't need
specialized classrooms like that
end up in this wing of
the cultural department.
They call it the old building.
This room's for
the literary club.
[KYON] So then it's the
literary club's room.
Yeah, I know, I know,
but this past spring
all the senior members left, so
now the club's got no members.
And if nobody else joins,
then that club's gonna be cut.
Oh, and this girl's
a new freshman member.
[KYON] So, the club
hasn't been cut then.
It's the same difference.
Besides, she's
the only one here.
But what're we gonna
do with her?
She told me that
she wouldn't mind it.
You sure about that?
[HARUHI] When I saw her
at lunch, I asked her
if we could use the club room.
She said go ahead.
She doesn't really care as long
as she has a place to read.
I guess some folks are just
strange like that, you know?
[KYON]
Look who's talking...
Yuki Nagato...
[KYON]
Miss... Nagato, was it?
You understand my colleague
here wants to use this room
for some other type of club.
Are you okay with that?
I'm fine.
You are?
O-Okay, but I'm pretty
sure we're gonna end up
causing you a lot
of trouble though.
No problem.
But someday you might get
kicked out of this room.
Go ahead.
[HARUHI]
Well, there you have it!
From now on, we're gonna
meet here in this room
right after school.
And ya better show up, mister,
'cause if you don't
it's the death penalty!
Understood.
[KYON]
I don't wanna die.
We need to find club members.
We're gonna need at
least two more people.
[KYON] What, that means
you already have that
literary club girl included
in the head count?
Does Haruhi think she
comes with the room
like some kind of accessory?
Don't worry,
I'll get 'em in no time.
I gotta couple leads on some
random people I can bring in.
[school bell chimes]
[KYON]
And so, the next day...
I'll meet ya there!
[KYON]
I guess I had no choice.
I found myself shuffling
over to the club room.
[KYON]
So, whatcha readin'?
Is it interesting?
Unique.
[KYON]
So, what part's unique?
All of it.
[KYON]
Huh, you really like books.
A little...
[KYON]
I see...
Can I go home now?
Sorry about that!
I'm a little late today
'cause it took me
forever to catch her.
[KYON] It was another girl.
A really beautiful girl.
What is this? Where am I?
W-Why did you bring me here?
Who are you people anyway?
Why are you locking the door?!
What do you want from me?!
[HARUHI]
Just be quiet.
Allow me to introduce
Mikuru Asahina.
[whimpers]
[HARUHI]
Hmm.
[KYON]
So much for introductions.
Where did you kidnap her from?
I didn't kidnap anyone,
she came here on her own.
[KYON]
Same difference.
I caught this one
daydreaming her brains out
in the junior's classroom.
During recess,
I make it a point
to walk every inch
of the main building.
I remembered seeing her around
a couple of times, and, well,
here she is.
[KYON] So that's why I haven't
seen her during recess.
Unbelievable.
Uh, hang on a second,
did you say she was a junior?
Well, so what if she is?
Yeah... Um, it's
Miss Asahina, wasn't it?
Why pick her of all people then?
What're you, blind?
Just look at her!
She's a total little cutie!
[KYON] Great. Now she
sounds like a pervert.
In this situation,
moe is an important
concept to keep in mind.
[KYON]
Sorry, what'd you say?
Moe! Moe!
This girl's a prime
example of moe.
It's a rule that in stories
with strange things going on,
you need to have
one moe character.
Someone with glasses
or in a maid costume,
or anything fetish-y.
It's essential.
And that's just the beginning!
[screams]
[HARUHI] She's tiny, but she's
got bigger breasts than me!
I mean, look at these things!
They're immense!
This is another important
aspect of moe!
[KYON]
Indeed...
[HARUHI]
Man, these suckers are huge!
It kinda pisses me off.
I mean, she's so cute
and her boobies
are ginormous compared to mine.
What're you, an idiot?
But they're totally
huge! Really!
You wanna feel 'em for yourself?
I think I'm gonna pass.
So Haruhi, you brought
this girl, Miss Asahina,
all the way up here just
because she happens to be
cute, tiny, and extremely
well-endowed?
Is that what you're
trying to tell me?
That's right!
[KYON]
She truly is an idiot.
I figured what the club needs
more than anything is a mascot.
Mikuru, are you a member of any
other school clubs right now?
The calligraphy club...
Oh, you can quit that one.
It'll just get in the way
of our club's activities.
Well...
Okay...
I understand...
[KYON]
What did she understand?
I'm going to quit
the calligraphy club
and join this one.
However, I don't really know
what the literary club does,
could you at least tell me that?
We're not the
literary club, Mikuru.
Huh?
We're sorta borrowing this
clubroom for now,
and the group you're about
to join is something
that Suzumiya is
gonna be starting up,
and so far she hasn't figured
out a name and has
absolutely no idea what we're
gonna be doing here anyway.
Oh, and by the way, the girl
siting over there
reading the book is the real
literary club member.
Oh...
Okay, I've got it!
I just figured out what we're
gonna call ourselves!
Well, spit it out.
May I have your
attention please.
The name of the hereto for
nameless start up club
has just been decided
and its name is...
The SOS Brigade!
[KYON] The "Spreading Excitement
All Over the World
With Haruhi Suzumiya Brigade."
The SOS Brigade for short.
Yeah... It's okay to laugh now.
[KYON] Actually, the name
should be something like,
"Spreading Excitement
All Over the World
With Haruhi Suzumiya
Organization,"
but we don't have the right
to form an organization yet.
And we still don't know what
the point of this club is.
Brigade'll have to
do then, won't it?
[KYON] And with that
baffling statement,
the name of the club
was decided.
Yay...
Just do whatever you want.