[KYON]
Something's... wrong.
That's what it felt like anyway.
[KYON] The game on TV
was between schools from
another town. Now, I had nothing
to do with either school,
but because I tend to
sympathize with underdogs,
I found myself routing
for the losing team.
And right about then,
I suddenly got the feeling
Haruhi was gonna call.
[phone ringing]
[KYON groans]
Your phone's ringing, Kyon.
[KYON]
I know, I know.
[phone ringing]
[HARUHI]
Hey, you're free, right?
Good, meet us at 2:00 o'clock
in front of the station.
Don't be late!
[dial tone]
[KYON] I didn't even have
the chance to say anything.
[phone ringing]
[KYON]
Hm?
[KYON'S SISTER]
It's your phone again.
[KYON]
Yeah, I know.
Now what?
[HARUHI] I forgot to
tell you, make sure to
bring your swim trunks,
and some money, too.
And your bike.
Definitely bring your bike.
That's it! Over and out!
[dial tone]
Huh?
[KYON] It was like I knew
what Haruhi was gonna say
before she said it.
Yeah, no.
Actually, it felt like
we had the exact
same conversation before.
Like déjà vu or something.
[COMMENTATOR]
...straight for left field.
And it's over the fence.
Another home run.
That makes is eight for Jyonan.
Well, you're late, Kyon!
Where's your motivation, huh?
Yeah, yeah. I'm sorry
if I kept you waiting.
No worries, I just got here too.
And now that we're all present
and accounted for, we can go!
[KYON]
Where?
The public pool!
Where do you think?
[KYON]
Yeah, that figures.
[HARUHI] We've got lots and lots
of summer vacationy things to do
during our break,
we've only so much time,
and once it's gone,
it's gone for good.
So we're gonna do everything
we can while we can
during our only summer
as tenth graders.
And for starters, we're gonna
ride the bikes to the pool.
[KYON] Did everyone
ride their bikes today?
No. The only bikes we have
are the ones you and I brought.
Okay, you guys. Are you ready?
Is anyone ever ready?
I'm good to go.
Don't let Koizumi
beat you, okay, Kyon?
Full speed ahead!
[KYON grunts]
Damn it!
[KYON panting]
[HARUHI]
Kyon.
We're trying to have fun,
so stop acting tired.
You're such a slacker.
[KYON]
And whose fault is that, huh?
[HARUHI]
Ah. Can you smell the chlorine?
That really makes
it feel like summer.
Come on, it's time
for a swim! I'll race ya!
[CHILDREN yelping]
[KYON] Can't you see
the no diving sign?
Hurry up and get in!
Come on! The water's
all warm and perfect!
[KYON groans]
Well, you have to admit, that
certainly does look like fun.
I mean, seeing Miss Suzumiya
enjoy herself in a normal way,
it's rather charming,
don't you think?
As long as Miss
Suzumiya's laughing
and just havin' a good time,
we don't have to worry about any
earth-shattering events, do we?
[KYON]
Hm. I hope you're right.
Is something wrong?
Hey, Koizumi.
Don't know. Maybe it's
just my imagination.
But with everything that's
happened since we met,
you could say that I've
become slightly paranoid.
Come on, let's go for a swim.
Hey!
[KYON]
[HARUHI]
Take that!
[HARUHI giggling]
[HARUHI]
Come back!
[KYON] Jeez. Now I know
why they call it a "public"
swimming pool. Seems like
everyone in town's here today.
[KYON]
Hm? Uh.
[KYON gasps]
That's weird.
It's like I've seen
this happen once before.
With Nagato looking
kind of bored like that.
And then...
[HARUHI]
Kyon!
[KYON] Uh-huh. And then
Haruhi shows up and she says...
[HARUHI] These two guys
are my brigade members,
they do what I say,
so if you want
something, ask them.
[HARUHI]
It's time to have some fun!
Come on! Let's go
play water soccer!
[KYON] Oh well.
Sometimes déjà vu's happen.
[HARUHI]
Here I go, Mikuru!
[MIKURU]
Okay!
--[HARUHI grunts]
--[MIKURU yelps]
[HARUHI]
Sorry!
[KYON]
What's that for?
[HARUHI] I got thinking
about some of the fun things
we could be doing. So I
came up with this schedule
of how we're going to spend
the rest of our vacation.
Just think about it,
we've only got two more
weeks before it's over.
And even though we've
done a lot up till now,
it still feels like
we've got a lot to do.
Since we've only got a
little bit of time left,
I made this list so we
could pick up the pace.
Is there anything you
want to do, Mikuru?
[MIKURU] Umm... I'd like
to try goldfish scooping.
[HARUHI]
Okay! Goldfish scooping.
[KOIZUMU]
Could I see that?
Thank you.
[HARUHI] Does anyone know
if there's a bon festival
happening close by?
Or a firework show?
[KOIZUMU] I can check and
see if there's anything.
[HARUHI] Oh! Don't foget
about the goldfish scooping.
It's Mikuru's only request.
I'll get right on it, then.
Okay, Kyon! We're
starting tomorrow!
[phone ringing]
[KYON] The next morning, I was
waken from my peaceful slumber
by a call from Haruhi.
[KYON] She said they
found a bon festival.
It was happening tonight
at a park... somewhere.
[HARUHI] Mikuru and Yuki
say they don't have yukatas.
So I decided we're gonna go
out and buy some to wear
for tonight. I don't
have one either,
but I found a place in town
that sells them in
sets for really cheap.
And you guys get
to come with us!
[KYON groans]
[KYON] So, we went
to a clothing outlet.
Haruhi picked out yukatas
for Miss Asahina and Nagato.
Then, marched them straight
into the changing rooms.
After making us wait about an
hour or so, insert yawn here,
they finally emerged.
[gasps]
[KYON]
Excellent.
The three of you look
wonderful in those.
Of course we do! I
picked 'em out myself.
Especially Mikuru's.
[HARUHI squeals]
Look at you. You're so
cute. I'm a genius.
Uh... Uh, thanks.
[KYON]
Miss Asahina, you look awesome!
[KYON sighs]
It figures it'd be so crowded.
Huh?
[gasps]
There it is again. That feeling.
I haven't been to a
bon festival in a while,
but it feels like I
just went to one.
That tower.
Those vendors.
Weird.
[HARUHI]
Mikuru!
Come on! Look!
They've got goldfish
scooping just like you wanted!
Over here!
[MIKURU]
Oh, uh, okay!
How 'bout it, wanna
scoop some fish?
No, I think I'll pass.
Don't tell me you're actually
into this kinda stuff.
Which one? It's on me.
No.
That.
Righty-o!
[KYON] I wish she would've
let me buy that for her.
It's the least I could do
after all she's done for us.
[HARUHI]
I caught 13 fish!
It's like the most
unbelievable haul ever!
But I don't have any
place to keep 'em all,
so I kept one and gave
the other to Mikuru.
Oh? Yuki? What's up?
What's with the mask?
[NAGATO]
I bought it.
Okay.
[KYON]
Hm?
[HARUHI]
I need your back for a second.
[KYON]
Why?
[HARUHI]
Just turn around.
Hey, don't!
[HARUHI] Fireworks!
That's what we're gonna do next!
We'll have a firework
show to end the day!
[KYON]
Do you even understand
the meaning of the
word moderation?
[KYON] It was summer,
and summer vacation.
And I guess that's why I
wanted to forget about it.
But the truth was, I couldn't
ignore it any longer.
Okay, everyone. Tomorrow,
we're gonna go catch some bugs.
It's the SOS Brigade
cicada catching contest!
And whoever catches the
most bugs tomorrow in gonna
get to be brigade
leader for one whole day!
Haruhi, I don't
wanna spoil your fun,
but have you finished
your homework yet?
[HARUHI]
Huh?
You're kidding me, right?
That stuff's totally easy.
You can finish it
in like three days.
You have to get
rid of that junk first
so you can spend the rest
of your summer having fun
and not worrying about it.
That's the only way
to really get the most
out of your vacation.
[MIKURU]
Wow.
[KYON] Why does she
have to be so smart?
[KYON] The next day was
beautiful, sunny and bright.
In fact, it was the perfect day
to have our SOS Brigade
cicada catching contest.
And although everyone caught
bugs the best way they knew how,
the winner of the contest ended
up being, you guessed it,
Haruhi.
[KYON]
We met the next day,
even though we had no
idea what was going on.
Our cluelessness continued as we
were made to wear frog costumes
and hand balloons out in front
of the local supermarket.
Welcome to our part-time job.
[KYON grunts]
Is everything okay down there?
I thought I was gonna die!
[HARUHI] Thanks for all the hard
work, especially in this heat.
The manager's super
grateful for everything.
Who the hell cares how grateful
he is. What about our pay?
This is it.
I've had my eye on
this guy for a while.
The manager gave it to us,
'cause Mikuru looked
so darn cute in it.
[KYON] That's what
we worked so hard for?
Mikuru, you have my permission
to wear 'em whenever you want.
Isn't he awesome?
[KYON]
Ribbit.
[phone ringing]
[KYON]
Later that night,
my peaceful slumber was
interrupted by a phone call.
[KYON]
Ugh, damn it.
[phone ringing]
[KYON]
Hello.
[MIKURU crying]
[KYON yelping]
[MIKURU]
Kyon...
Is that you, Miss Asahina?
[MIKURU]
Yes, it's me.
Something really bad...
I don't know...
What's wr--?
[KOIZUMU]
Hello. It's Koizumi.
Why are you with Miss Asahina
in the middle of the night?!
[KOIZUMU]
We have a situation here.
Is it possible for you to
come meet us right now?
[KYON]
Of course! I'll be right over!
[KYON grunting]
[MIKURU crying]
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[KYON]
Miss Asahina, what happened?
It's terrible, Kyon.
I can't go back to
the future anymore!
[MIKURU crying]
You can't go back?
But you're...
What are you saying?
I'll explain it the best I can.
We're currently
stuck in a time loop
that seems to have no end to it.
[KYON]
Huh? A what?
We're currently
stuck in a time loop
that seems to have no end to it.
[KYON]
Uh.
We're currently
stuck in a time loop
that seems to have no end--
[KYON]
Come on, Koizumi.
Do you realize
what you just said?
Yes, of course I do.
And much more than I
want to, believe me.
Earlier, I was having a
word with Miss Asahina.
[KYON]
Call me, next time.
[KOIZUMU] And that was
when we both realized
something seemed a little off
about the current flow of time.
Actually, Miss Asahina was
the one discovered it first.
Thanks to her, my suspicions
were confirmed.
Suspicions?
We've been reliving the
same period of time
over and over again, stuck in an
infinite time loop without
any way of getting unstuck.
I know, you already said that.
We've been repeating
every single day
between August the
17th through the 31st,
and have become stuck
right in the middle
of what seems to be an
endless summer vacation.
Well, we're definitely in
the middle of something.
It's a never-ending, endless
summer to be precise.
The future doesn't exist
in this world any longer.
All time stops at
September the 1st.
And that's the
reason Miss Asahina
can't travel back to the future.
It's only natural that she
can't return to a future
that no longer exists.
Are you kidding me?
There's nothing natural
about a concept like that.
Who's gonna believe
such nonsense?
For starters, we were
sort of hoping you would.
Hey, guys.
I think I can try to explain it.
Here I go...
Because I have to
classify information,
I used classified information
to get in touch with the future.
The thing is,
I haven't gotten any classified
information for a week.
So we started to think
how weird that was.
I was so surprised.
I classified information,
I really did...
[KYON]
Oh, Miss Asahina.
Are the classified information
things you're talking about
Stuff you can't say on TV?
So, what about
those closed spaces
you were talking about before?
Is it possible we're trapped
in something like that?
No, it's not one of those.
A specific section of
time has been torn away.
At exactly midnight on August
the 31st, everything resets,
and then time
reverts straight back
to the morning
of August the 17th.
That's the process.
What about our...?
Wait, what about the
whole world's memories?
Their memory resets as well.
Everyone's memory starts
over from the beginning again.
Perfect. It's another
problem involving time.
[KYON sighs]
Well, I guess I shouldn't
be surprised about that.
No, Miss Asahina doesn't
have anything to do with it.
Okay. What does?
Miss Suzumiya does.
[KYON groans]
Somewhere deep down inside her,
there's a desire to have
summer vacation last forever,
and I'm sure she
doesn't even realize it.
No way.
Are you saying she still
hasn't had enough fun?
That's what it looks like to me.
Perhaps she feels there's
something else
that needs to happen
before our summer
vacation can really be over.
[KYON sighs]
Oh man.
The trouble she gets us into
is always galactic in scale.
You know, you're acting
like you're enjoying this
an awful lot, you
wanna tell me why?
Please don't take
that the wrong way,
but this explains the feelings
of déjà vu I've been having.
And looking back on it now,
they were most likely the
residue of my memories
whenever time had been reset.
You've been feeling
them too, haven't you?
Are we the only ones, or
can other people feel it, too?
[KOIZUMU]
Mh-hm.
It looks like you and I are
exceptions to the rule.
The only people who can
sense this strange feeling
would be the ones who are
the closest to Miss Suzumiya.
Then what about Haruhi?
Does she even know this
stuff's even happening?
No, I don't think
she really does.
Besides, I think
it would be very,
very bad for us if she did.
But... there's someone else.
Someone who isn't
affected by the time loop
or the feelings of déjà vu
we've been experiencing.
They remember it all.
Really? And who
would that person be?
I think you know who it is.
[KYON gasps]
Nagato. Is that the truth?
It is.
And you can remember everything?
I can.
Then, can you tell me how many
times this has happened so far?
This would be 15,499 times.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON] Fifteen thousand,
four-hundred ninety-nine?
What do you mean 15,499?
What are you saying, Nagato?
Okay, are you being
totally serious?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
So, what you're saying we've
done the exact same things
every time that many times?
[NAGATO]
Not necessarily.
Throughout 15,499 repetitions,
we did not attend a bon
festival the 2,391st time
and the 11,054th time.
We went to a bon
festival but did not go
to a fish scooping
booth 437 times.
We obtained part-time
jobs 9,026 times
and worked six different jobs.
In addition to
handing out balloons,
we worked as movers, cashiers,
we handed out flowers,
worked as--
I got it. That's enough.
[KYON] Fifteen thousand,
four-hundred ninety-nine times.
That's what she said. Times two
weeks. That's... 594 years.
She's the only one who
remembers everything we did.
And she's had to repeat
them over and over again.
Nagato.
What's it like to relive the
same things that many times?
That's gotta be the
craziest story ever.
[KYON] The next night,
we went stargazing.
We were on the balcony
of Nagato's apartment
and Koizumi brought
the telescope.
[HARUHI groans]
I'm getting bored.
I'm gonna look for UFOs now.
[KYON] Uh! Hey! Haruhi,
you'll break it! Wait! Stop!
Don't spin it like that!
[KYON] I wish I knew
what else she wants to do.
[KOIZUMI] Well now, that's
the all-important question,
isn't it? If we knew the answer,
we could solve this problem.
I've got an idea,
how 'bout we try this?
What if someone were to suddenly
grab Miss Suzumiya from behind
and then they whispered,
"I love you" right into her ear.
And who's going
to be doing this?
Who else could play
that role other than you?
Well, you can count me out then!
All right. How 'bout
if I give it a try?
[chuckles]
No, I'm just kidding.
I really don't think I
can pull it off anyway.
And besides, it would just end
up confusing Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON sighs]
[KYON]
We kept chugging along,
doing all kinds of
summer vacation things.
We went to the batting cages,
to a real firework show,
and we even signed up for
a goby fishing tournament.
We did the "test of courage."
Watched some movies,
went to the beach,
bowling, and karaoke.
Yup, we were always
doing somethin'.
[KYON] And the whole time,
all I could think was that
none of it was going
to be enough for Haruhi.
But what could I do
about it? Nothing.
So, I just bit my lip
and watched as the last days of
our summer vacation went by.
And then, before I knew it,
August the 30th was here.
Again.
[HARUHI] That's it, we've done
everything on our list.
[HARUHI sighs]
But now I'm wonder
if we did enough.
Eh, oh well, I guess
we got to do a lot.
Hey, does anyone wanna
do anything else?
Oh, okay.
I guess we did everything that
we set out to do this summer,
so that's good enough.
[KYON]
No, it's not, Haruhi.
Not by a long shot.
You're still not satisfied.
--[HARUHI chuckles]
--[KYON gasps]
Okay, guys, we're
done for today.
I set tomorrow
aside just in case,
but I guess you can
take the day off now.
I'll see you all at the
club room on Monday.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
Wait, Haruhi!
There's that feeling again.
And it's way stronger
than all the others.
I can't let Haruhi leave.
If I let her walk out that door,
we'll end up reliving the past
two weeks again and again
for a thousand more times.
But... what should I do?
What should I say?
There must've been a clue
in something Haruhi said,
but what was it?
What's she been
saying all this time?
[KYON]
I don't know...
Can't remember.
[KYON]
It's August the 31st.
I haven't touched my homework.
[KYON sighs]
Whatever. It doesn't matter.
There isn't any
point in doing it.
We're just gonna keep reliving
the last couple of
weeks over again.
[yawns]
[KYON] Whatever happens next,
whether tomorrow comes or not,
a different version of me
will have to deal with it.