[KYON] Self-proclaimed humanoid
interface created by aliens.
Self-proclaimed
time travelling girl.
squad of ESPer boys.
They've shown me enough
proof that I may now
safely remove the words
"self-proclaimed"
from their titles.
The three of them, each for
their own reasons, mind you,
are currently focused
on Haruhi Suzumiya.
Even if I believe
everything I've seen,
I still can't figure
out one thing:
Why me?
An alien? A girl from the
future, and an ESPer boy
all migrated toward Haruhi
because, as Koizumi put it,
that's what she wished for.
What about me?
Why have I been
dragged feet-first
into all of this
weird stuff anyway?
I mean, I'm a 100%
ordinary high schooler.
No special powers
or anything here.
I mean, who wrote this scenario?
Was it you, Haruhi?
Yeah, right. It's not like
it's my problem anyway.
Why do I have to get all
worked up about it?
All of this is Haruhi's fault.
Seriously, she's the one
who should be worried
about all of this
weirdness going on, not me.
Nagato, Koizumi, Miss Asahina...
From now on, they should just
go speak to her directly,
and whatever happens after that,
well, that's Haruhi's problem.
I've got nothing to do with it.
Everyone else can go do
whatever they want
as far as I'm concerned.
Yo.
Hey.
[KYON] Taniguchi, do you think
I'm a normal high schooler?
[TANIGUCHI]
Huh?
I don't know. Normal high
schoolers don't go around
pushing girls down
in classrooms,
know what I'm sayin'?
Especially Yuki Nagato, who,
according to my ranking system,
scores about A-.
[KYON] I shall explain myself.
Taniguchi's memory of the events
was a complete fiction;
a fantasy, merely a dream.
Nagato's the victim of Haruhi,
who's turned the Literary Club
into her lair. Upset by
this turn of events,
she merely consulted
me for advice.
I sympathize with the poor girl,
and agreed to help out
as best as I could.
After Haruhi'd gone, we'd
decided to meet in the classroom
so that we could
discuss her options.
That's when Nagato,
an anemic all her life,
suffered a seizure.
She toppled over, and as
I lunged to prevent her
from falling to the
hard, linoleum floor,
you came walking through
the door, Taniguchi.
Once you find out the
truth about something,
ten to one, it's
always gonna turn out
to be something trivial.
You liar.
Tch..
Even if I was dumb enough
to believe that lie,
the fact that Nagato,
who's famous for being
anti-social, mind you,
came to you for advice?
Well, that automatically
makes you not normal, buddy.
I never realized
Nagato's that famous.
[TANIGUCHI] Also, you happen to
be one of Suzumiya's henchman.
So if you think that
you're just a normal,
male high school student,
then I'm about as normal
as a water flea.
Hey, Taniguchi, you don't have
any supernatural powers, do you?
Huh?
I knew it. You've finally
become poisoned by Suzumiya's
extreme brand of
nuttiness, haven't you?
Don't get too
close to me, buddy,
or I'll catch the Suzumiya bug.
[laughs]
Why didn't you change
outta your gym clothes?
Because it's hot.
[KYON]
Hm.
[HARUHI] Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna change again
when we get to the clubroom
Besides, I've got cleaning
duty and it's easier
for me to move around in this.
[KYON] Yeah, well,
can't argue with that.
[HARUHI]
I was thinking, what do you want
Mikuru's next costume to be?
[KYON] Hm... We've had
the bunny girl, the maid...
I guess she could--
Wait, what do you mean next?!
[HARUHI] Kitty cat ears? Or a
nurse? Or maybe a dominatrix...
[KYON] Kitty cat ears... Nurse's
outfit... Maybe a dominatrix...
What an idiot.
[KYON] Hey, you're the
one who brought it up.
[HARUHI]
Oh man... I'm so bored...
[KYON]
I see... There it is.
[MIKURU] You working
on anything important?
[KYON]
No, nothing.
Really? Hey, what's this?
[KYON gasps]
I'm screwed!
Why does that folder
have my name on it, huh?
Come on, let me see,
let me see, let me see!
[KYON] Oh, this? Well,
yeah, I warned her.
It's probably nothing
to worry about, though.
[MIKURU]
That sounds like a lie.
[KYON] Miss Asahina, could you
step back a little, please?
Please let me look. Can't I see?
Let me look!
--Come on, please?
--[door opens]
[HARUHI] What do you
two think you're doing?
Uh...
[HARUHI] So, you're into
maid outfits, huh?
What're you talking about?
We're gonna change.
Sure, fine with me.
I said we're changing now!
So what?
[growls] Get out now!
[KYON yells]
[KYON]
What's with her?
She never cares if people
see her when she's changing
in our homeroom...
Well, now my arms
and shoulders are cool,
but the rest of this crummy
outfit doesn't breathe at all!
[KOIZUMI]
Hello?
So I guess today's the
day of the costume party?
[KYON] Don't make this
story more complicated.
[HARUHI]
Mikuru.
Come here. Have a seat.
[whimpers]
They're like a
couple of sisters.
[KYON] She just wants to
make a maid with braids.
[KYON]
In the end, it was actually
a pretty normal day at the club.
[MIKURU whimpers]
[KYON] There wasn't really
anything we wanted to do.
Actually, we didn't
know what we should do.
It was like a
moratorium on life:
As time flowed by, the life
we took for granted,
an ordinary life.
And despite feeling dissatisfied
about the overwhelming lack
of things to do, you keep
thinking about the next day.
You keep telling yourself
you still got lots of time.
[KYON sighs] But that was
unusual in and of itself.
And it really wasn't
a bad thing at all.
Almost getting killed by a
classmate, or perhaps meeting
a monster tearing up a deserted
world with gray skies.
Now, those things don't
happen every day.
It's true, I wished that days
like this would last forever,
and wouldn't you
think that way, too?
But there was someone
that didn't think so.
And, of course,
it was Haruhi Suzumiya.
--[door opens]
--[KYON'S SISTER hums]
What d'you think you're doing?
Scissors! I need 'em
for art class.
Well, okay, I guess,
but just ask for 'em
next time, all right?
[KYON] She knew that she
could get away with it.
[KYON] By the way, do you what
makes people have dreams?
There are two kinds
of sleep: REM sleep,
and then there's non-REM sleep.
The two repeat in intervals
throughout the sleep cycle.
During REM, when the body's
asleep, but the brain is still
somewhat active, that's
when we have dreams.
--[HARUHI] Kyon. Kyon!
--[claps]
[KYON] The alarm hasn't
gone off yet, has it?
--[HARUHI] Wake up!
--[clapping]
[KYON]
No way.
[HARUHI]
I'm telling you to wake up!
[gasps]
Do you know where
we are right now?
[HARUHI]
I thought I woke up,
and then I found
myself in this place
with you lying there,
passed out next to me.
What's going on?
And why did we wake up
outside our school like this?
[KYON]
A closed space.
I thought I was sleeping
in my bed at home,
so how did we end up
in this place?
The sky, it's weird.
Have you seen Koizumi?
No, why? Is he here?
No, just a hunch I had.
[KYON grunts]
First off, let's get
out of the school.
We might be able to find
someone somewhere else.
You don't seem very surprised
by all of this somehow.
[KYON]
Oh, I'm surprised all right.
Especially at the fact
that you're here.
[BOTH grunt]
What is this?
[KYON grunts]
This thing runs all around
the perimeter of the school.
Does that mean we
can't get out of here?
Well, if you're scared,
just go ahead and grab my arm,
why don'tcha? I'm sure it
will help get me in the mood.
Jerk.
I can't get a dial tone.
[KYON]
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Hey, Kyon, look.
[HARUHI]
Where are we...?
It's really weird...
You thirsty?
[HARUHI]
No thanks.
What's going on? What is this?
I don't get it at all.
Where are we? And why
am I here anyway?
And on top of all that,
why am I alone with you?
[KYON]
How should I know?
I'm gonna look around.
You stay here, got it?
I'll be right back.
[door creaks]
[KYON]
Typical Haruhi behavior.
Koizumi, that you?
[KOIZUMI]
Well, hello there.
Took you long enough to show up.
Although I guess I was sort
of expecting to see you
looking a little more normal.
[KOIZUMI] Yeah, that. I need to
talk to you about something.
Frankly speaking, this is what
I'd call an emergency situation.
Normally, I can get into closed
space without too much trouble,
but this time, even with some
extra power from my colleagues,
it was all I could do to show up
in this incomplete form,
and I'm not gonna
last too long either.
Looks like our ESPer
powers are fading.
They could disappear
any minute now.
Then, do you know
what's going on?
And are Haruhi and I the
only ones stuck in here?
[KOIZUMI] That's it, the
thing we've been afraid of
happening all along is
starting to happen right now.
It seems Miss Suzumiya's finally
given up on the real world.
She's decided to
create a new one now.
In other words, this is
the end of the world.
[KYON]
What was that?!
[KOIZUMI] The top brass
at the organization
is seriously panicked right now.
Nobody knows what will
happen to the real world
now that we've lost our deity.
If Miss Suzumiya's feeling
merciful, we might get to keep
living on this
side of the bubble.
But it might disappear into
nothing the next minute, too.
[KYON]
Wait, now why's this--
[KOIZUMI] Who knows? In any
case, both you and Miss Suzumiya
have completely disappeared
from our world.
You two aren't in an
ordinary closed space.
It's a new dimension that
Miss Suzumiya's created.
I dunno. Maybe all the other
closed spaces were practice
for the one you're in right now.
[KOIZUMI] The space that
you're in right now
is probably the world
that Miss Suzumiya
wishes she was in.
I don't really know what
she wants, so, I'm at a loss
as to what could happen next.
Do you have any idea why
I'm the one in here with her?
[KOIZUMI]
You honestly have no idea why?
You were chosen
by Miss Suzumiya.
You were the one and only
person from the other world
that Miss Suzumiya
really wanted to be with.
I thought you'd have
realized that by now.
[KOIZUMI] Looks like
I'm almost out of time.
Way things are going,
I don't think
we'll be seeing
each other again.
So you're telling me that's it?
I gotta live all alone here
with Haruhi in this
dull world of gray?
[KOIZUMI]
You're the new Adam and Eve.
Go on, procreate and
increase the population.
[KYON]
I'll punch you for that.
[KOIZUMI] Just joking. It's
only a theory, but I think
in a little while,
this place will start
looking more familiar.
However, it's not going to be
exactly the same as over here.
Well, if I ever get
reincarnated on your side,
be sure to say hi for me.
So we can never go back
to that side ever again?
[KOIZUMI]
Only if Miss Suzumiya wishes it.
Although I hate to say it, the
chances of that are pretty slim.
I'm gonna miss you guys a lot;
I would've liked to get to know
both of you better.
The whole thing fills me
with a bit of regret.
Oh! Almost forgot. I've got
messages for you from
Mikuru Asahina and Yuki Nagato.
Miss Asahina told me to
deliver an apology to you.
"I'm sorry, it's all my fault."
And Yuki Nagato told me to tell
you, "Turn on the computer."
Goodbye...
What kind of joke
is this anyway...?
[gasps]
[KYON]
'Course I can see it.
What should I do?
[KYON]
That what?
Nagato!
What do you want me to do...?
Nagato... Koizumi...
[rumbling]
Kyon! Something's here!
What is it?! A monster?!
It's not an illusion, is it?!
Maybe it's an alien?!
Or is it some kind of
super weapon that a race
of ancient people created that's
been awakened in our world?!
[HARUHI]
What're you doing?!
[HARUHI screams]
That thing's not trying
to attack us, is it?
What're we running
away from it for?
I don't think it's
evil or anything.
Who knows?
[crashing]
[HARUHI]
Do you know what's happening?
This weird world,
and that giant...
[KYON] Don't you wanna go back
to the world we used to be in?
Huh...?
[KYON] We can't stay in a
place like this forever.
I mean, if we get hungry,
there aren't any places
to eat here.
[HARUHI] It's strange,
but I have a feeling
we'll get by somehow.
I'm having fun right now.
I wonder why...?
[KYON] What're you going
to do with the SOS Brigade?
You created it. Are you
just gonna throw it away?
[HARUHI]
It doesn't matter anymore.
I'm having the strangest,
most wonderful experience
I've ever dreamed of having!
I don't need to search for it
when it's happening right here.
But I wanna go back!
[gasps]
[KYON] It took something like
this to make me realize:
Even though I complain a lot,
I really liked my life
up till now. Kunikida,
and that idiot Taniguchi...
Koizumi, Nagato, Miss Asahina...
And that Asakura girl
who disappeared,
you could put her
on the list, too.
What're you talking about?
I wanna go back and
see all of them again.
I don't know, I feel like
I've still got so many things
that I wanna talk to them about.
You'll see them again.
It's not like this place
is gonna be covered by a big,
gloomy shadow forever.
Once tomorrow comes
around, I'm positive
the sun's gonna shine again.
I know it will, I can tell!
That's not it. I'm not talking
about seeing them in here,
I wanna see everybody
from the old world
in the old world.
I don't understand you...
Weren't you sick and tired
of the boring world
we were living in?!
Didn't you want something
really weird and interesting
to happen like I did?!
[KYON]
I used to.
You know something, Haruhi?
For the last couple days, I've
had all these strange things
happening around me.
You had no way of knowing this,
but I guess you could say
the world's been
revolving around you.
You've been completely
unaware of it,
but actually, everything
in the world was getting
more and more weird
and interesting.
[crashing]
[KYON] Nagato said she was
the potential for evolution.
Miss Asahina called her a
distortion in space time.
And Koizumi treated
her like a god.
Then, what about me?
What does Haruhi Suzumiya
mean to someone like me?
Haruhi is Haruhi,
nothing else but Haruhi.
Great, using tautology
to dodge the question.
I can't help it, I just don't
have a definite answer for it.
I mean, think about it.
If somebody pointed at a
classmate of yours and asked you
what that person meant to you,
how would you answer?
What would you say?
Sorry, I'm dodging
the question again.
But to me, Haruhi
isn't just a classmate,
and of course, she's not
the potential for evolution,
a time distortion,
or a god either.
That's impossible!
[MIKURU] Do you know
the story of Snow White?
What's wrong?
I've sorta got a thing
for girls with ponytails.
What?
I don't remember when it was,
but you had your
hair in a ponytail,
and it looked so good
on you, it was criminal.
Huh?
What're you, an idiot?
[gasps]
[grunts]
What kinda dream was that?!
Sigmund Freud's gotta
be laughing at me!
[yelping]
[KYON] I never had a dream
that was so realistic before...
[yawns]
[KYON] Or maybe... Maybe this
isn't the old world anymore.
Maybe this world is a new
one that Haruhi created.
And if that's the case,
how would I go about
confirming it?
[KYON]
Yo.
How you doin'?
[HARUHI]
I dunno, not so good.
I had a nightmare last night.
Really?
[HARUHI] Yeah, I couldn't really
get any sleep because of it.
I've never wanted to ditch
school so badly like today.
Is that so?
Haruhi.
Yeah, what?
Looks good on you.
[KOIZUMI] I believe I should
be thanking you right now.
Looks like I get to
keep my part-time job
a little while longer.
Well, I don't think we can
deny the distinct possibility
that the world we're in
now was freshly created
by her last night. In any case,
it is an honor to see you
and Miss Suzumiya again.
Be seeing you after class.
You and Haruhi Suzumiya
disappeared from this world
for two hours and 30 minutes.
[KYON] So, tell me,
how many more of your kind
are out there anyway?
A lot.
[KYON] And, is somebody like
Asakura going to come around
and try and kill me again?
Don't worry.
I won't let that happen.
--Huh...?
--[gasps]
[whimpers]
Kyon, you're back!
[MIKURU sobs]
I'm so glad to see you again.
I thought... that you'd...
never make it back...
[KYON]
Miss Asahina...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
If Miss Suzumiya
saw this, it'll be like
birds of a feather repeating
their mistakes again!
I don't have any idea
what you're saying.
Oh, by the way, Miss Asahina,
I believe you've got a
star-shaped mole on your chest
right about here, am I right?
[MIKURU gasps]
H-How did you know that...?
I-I didn't even know it
was shaped like a star
till just now.
W-W-When did you realize it?
[HARUHI]
And what are you two doing?
Mikuru. I bet you're bored
with the maid outfit, so...
I gotcha a new one.
--[MIKURU] What? No!
--[HARUHI] Stop squirming!
[HARUHI]
Resistance is futile!
This time it's a nurse's outfit!
Or should I say doctor's aid?
Oh, whatever you
call 'em, it's cute!
[KYON] Now, let me tell you
about what happened afterwards.
The SOS Brigade
finally submitted
all the necessary paperwork
to register as an
extra-curricular group
within the school.
I was sure that the name
"Spreading Excitement All Over
the World With Haruhi Suzumiya
Brigade" would've been
rejected outright.
So we changed it at
the last minute to:
"Spreading Cheer to Our
Student Body Brigade."
And we still patrol the town
for strange phenomena.
Today's our second tour of duty.
By some strange
coincidence, Miss Asahina,
Nagato, and Koizumi
all had errands to run, so I'm
waiting for Haruhi by myself.
I made sure to arrive an hour
before we had agreed to meet.
Remember, we had a rule that
regardless of whether or not
you were late, the last person
to show up gets a penalty.
I'm not quite sure
why she's scowling.
Perhaps it's a reaction to
the low attendance rate today.
Or could it be regret
that she's shown up last?
I dunno.
But I'll have lots
of time to find out...
...when she's buying
me lunch at the café.
And when we sit down,
I'd like to talk to her
about all sorts of things.
About how the SOS Brigade is
going to operate from now on,
my wishlist for Miss Asahina's
cosplay, etc., etc.
But I digress.
I already know exactly
what I wanna talk
to her about first.
Yeah, that's right.
For starters,
I'm thinkin' I'd
like to talk to her
a little bit about aliens,
time travelers, and... ESPers.