You're... an alien?
[YUKI] My mission is to observe
Haruhi Suzumiya and report
the information back to the data
integration thought entity.
I've been performing
this task daily
since my creation
three years ago.
It has been quite peaceful
and there have been
no uncertain factors.
However, irregularities have
appeared near Haruhi Suzumiya
which cannot be ignored.
That would be... you.
[YUKI] To the data integration
thought entity,
the third planet in the
solar system, this planet,
held no special value.
However, the current inhabitants
of Earth as it is known
by your kind, developed
a cognitive ability
that could be
considered intelligence.
Consequently, the significance
of the planet increased.
There was the possibility
that your kind might
provide an answer in overcoming
the inert evolution
the entity is experiencing.
Throughout the universe, it is
common for organic lifeforms
to develop a consciousness.
Human beings from Earth
were the only creatures
whose consciences evolved
into intellect.
The entity carefully,
yet thoroughly,
continued its observations.
Three years ago, they noticed
an abnormal flare up of data
on the surface of the planet.
This explosion of information
started from one area
of a bow-shaped archipelago,
then quickly enveloped
the entire planet
and surged further
outward into space.
In the center of all this was...
For the three years since,
multiple investigations
and observations have occurred
regarding Haruhi Suzumiya.
However, she remains an enigma.
Regardless, one section
of the entity...
...continues to perform its
analysis of Haruhi Suzumiya.
The entity believes she will be
the key to human kind's
auto-evolution
as well as its own.
Because the entity is an
astro-being, it can not
directly communicate with
organic lifeforms.
The entity does not communicate
through language,
and your kind has no way of
communicating without language.
That is why the data
integration thought entity
created interfaces
such as myself.
Through me, it can make contact
with the human species.
[KYON]
Uh...
We believe that Haruhi Suzumiya
has the potential for
auto-evolution. She has
the power to manipulate
the environmental data
around her for her benefit.
That is the reason
why I am here,
and the reason why you are here.
[KYON]
Hold it. Just hang on a sec.
I'm totally lost.
Trust me...
Okay, first of all, why me?
I mean, for starters, let's just
say I believe all this stuff
you're tellin' me about
this data-integrated
whatchamahoozit thingy in space.
But if it's true, why reveal
your identity to me?
You have been chosen
by Haruhi Suzumiya.
Whether she knows it or not,
Haruhi Suzumi has the power
to affect her surroundings by
transforming her will into
absolute data. There is
a reason she chose you
rather than someone else.
No way.
Way.
You and Haruhi Suzumiya have
the possibilities in your hands.
You're serious about all this.
Of course.
[KYON] Here I am, amazed
that the silent one had
finally started talking,
but the stuff that was
coming out of her mouth
was completely whacko.
I never imagined she'd
be so... out there.
You know, you'd really make
Haruhi ecstatic if you
went up to her personally
and told her all this stuff.
Hate to say it, but I'm having a
hard time keeping up with this
kinda talk, it's so confusing.
The data integration thought
entity is under the impression
that if Haruhi Suzumiya
is made aware of her worth
and her abilities, it would
create a catastrophic event.
For now, we must continue our
observations unbeknownst to her.
Okay... but I could run out
right now and tell Haruhi
everything you just
explained to me.
[YUKI]
She does not take
the information you
feed her seriously.
That's true.
I am not the only interface
that the data integration
thought entity has placed
upon this planet.
Another section of the entity
is determined to use
more proactive methods
with Haruhi Suzumiya
in order to observe the
fluctuations of data.
You are the key to
Haruhi Suzumiya.
If there is danger,
you are the first target.
[KYON]
I'm outta here...
[police siren]
[KYON]
Humanoid inter... what?
Aliens.
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] She's always by
herself reading this stuff.
Maybe that's where her weird
fantasies come from.
I'll bet that when
she's in class
she doesn't talk to anybody.
She just stays cooped up
in her own little world.
Yuki and Haruhi need to
just chill out and enjoy
some plain, old ordinary
school life.
[HARUHI] I can't believe it!
He's finally here!
Isn't it amazing?!
Mysterious transfer student!
It's gotta be!
You haven't even seen him yet,
how do you know he's mysterious?
Like I said, a student who
transfers during this strange,
in-between time in the middle
of school has a good chance
of being a mysterious
transfer student!
If you don't mind,
I wanna know just who
gave you that statistic.
Because if it's true, and
you take into account all
the mysterious people in Japan,
then everyone would
be considered--
I'm gonna go check him out!
And, you're not listening,
are you?
[KYON] After school when
I stopped by the club,
Miss Asahina had heroically
recovered after only one day.
[KYON] I'm surprised
to see you back here
after everything that happened.
[MIKURU] Yeah, but after
thinking about it,
I realized I still had concerns.
[KYON] I could swear
she said that before...
[KYON]
What're you concerned about?
[MIKURU]
Um... It's nothing.
Huh?
You wanna sit in for a game?
So, Nagato,
you ever play Othello?
[MIKURU]
Uh...
[KYON]
Hmm?
[HARUHI]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Someone transferred into
freshman class 9 today,
and he's joining us!
His name is--
Itsuki Koizumi. How do you do?
This is the SOS Brigade!
I'm Haruhi Suzumiya
the Brigade leader,
and these are brigade
members numbers one,
two, and three!
By the way, you're
member number four.
Everyone should make him
feel right at home!
I don't mind joining you guys,
but I was wondering what
kind of club this is anyway.
Let me tell you exactly what the
SOS Brigade is all about.
Attention.
The SOS Brigade's mission
is to find aliens,
time travelers, and ESPers
and hang out with them!
[KYON]
It's as if the whole world
has come to a grinding halt.
No, not really.
But I was reminded of
Haruhi's declaration
on the first day of school.
Oh, I get it.
As expected from Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON]
What did he just get?
All right, I'll join your club,
and I hope to have a
good time with all of you.
[KYON] What? Even after
what she just said?
Was he even listening?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Itsuki Koizumi
and I just transferred here.
There's still a
lot I don't know,
so I hope you'll
show me the ropes.
Uh, yeah, um...
[HARUHI]
That's Kyon!
And the cute one is Mikuru!
And the one over there
with the glasses is Yuki.
Uh...
[screams]
Oh my, are you all right?
We've got five members now, and
that means we're an official
extracurricular club!
I'm fine, really. Thanks.
Yay! The time has finally come
for the SOS Brigade
to be unveiled!
For gaters, get ready to do
your best and fight as one!
[KYON] Fighting? Unveiled? And
now Nagato's become a member...
I mean, are you sure you're
okay with that, Nagato?
Moving right along, it's now
after school the following day.
[MIKURU]
Noooo!
[HARUHI] Come one, hurry up!
Take your clothes off!
--[MIKURU sobbing]
--[HARUHI laughs]
[screams]
Holy--!
Sorry!
[HARUHI] When it comes to moe,
the maid costume is essential.
You need one in every
school-based story.
What kind of school-based
story is this?
[HARUHI] And now...
it's time for pictures!
[gasps]
But... Don't take a picture!
[HARUHI]
Chin down a bit... Good.
Grab hold of the apron...
Bigger smile... Work it!
Kyon, take over for me, okay?
Mikuru, let's make
things a little sexier!
--What're you doing?!
--Come on, it's okay!
[KYON]
There's nothing okay about it.
Yeah, I should talk.
I'm the one taking the pictures.
[HARUHI]
Yuki, gimme your glasses.
Here we go!
[KYON]
And glasses are on.
What is she planning to do
with these photos anyway?
[HARUHI]
Yeah, perfect!
A glasses-wearing lolita
maid with great boobs!
This is so awesome!
Noo!
[HARUHI] From now on, Mikuru,
whenever you're in this room,
you gotta wear this outfit!
[MIKURU]
No...
Uh! What's going on here?
[HARUHI]
Oh, right! Now we're talkin'!
Let's all have some
fun with Mikuru!
[KYON]
That's enough.
Thanks for the offer,
but I'll pass.
I'd be afraid of
the consequences.
Please continue though.
Don't mind me.
[KYON] I could use
a little help here...
Haven't you had enough?
Just cut it out already.
You've gotta be breaking
several laws here.
What're you talkin' about?!
Whatever...
I got a lot of photos anyway.
[HARUHI] Okay, the very first
meeting of the SOS Brigade
is about to begin!
We did a lot to come
this far this fast.
We passed out flyers,
we made a website,
and now, we see that the SOS
Brigade's fame at this school
has sky rocketed!
Sure, you could say...
[KYON] I wonder what part of
"traumatizing Miss Asahina"
makes this a big success?
[HARUHI] However, we haven't
gotten a single email
concerning strange phenomena.
Also, not even one student's
come by yet to consult us
about anything weird or...
[KYON]
Yeah, go figure.
I mean, it's not exactly clear
what we're even
supposed to be doing.
After all, we just found out
what this club's for yesterday.
[HARUHI]
People like to say stuff like,
"Good things come
to those who wait."
But in these times,
we cannot sit and wait!
We must find those good things
even if we have to dig up
every inch of this Earth!
So then, let's go
search for them!
For what?
The mysteries of this world!
[KYON] And with that, we are now
going on a tour around the city
in search of mystery
and phenomena.
On Saturday, meet at 9 am in
front of Kitaguchi Station.
Those who arrive late shall
receive the death penalty.
Death penalty...?
You know, I really hate
to waste a day off...
You're late! Penalty!
[KYON] Haruhi's proposal:
Split off into groups of two,
search the city for
mysterious phenomena.
If we find any, alert
the others via cell phone.
That is all.
I guess we got our groups.
[KYON] It might be a lucky
day for me after all.
I mean, if I can go on
a date with Miss Asahina,
treating everyone to lunch
'cause I was late
is a small price to pay.
[HARUHI]
Kyon, are you paying attention?
Would you be serious here?
This isn't a date, got it?
[KYON]
Yeah, I hear ya.
Look, this isn't fun and games!
You mess around
and I'll kill ya!
[KYON] And with those parting
words, Haruhi's team left
to investigate the east side of
the station while Miss Asahina
and I were ordered to search the
west side. However...
What should we do?
[KYON]
Beats me.
[MIKURU]
This is the first time
I've ever gone for
a walk like this.
By like this, you mean...?
Out walking alone with a boy.
Oh!
Come on, I can't believe that.
You're telling me that you've
never gone out on a date
with anyone before?
[MIKURU]
Never.
Hah, you're kidding, right?
I mean, don't you have guys
just lining up to ask you out?
Mm. But... I can't do it.
You see, I'm not supposed to
go out on dates with anyone.
At least not in this--
[gasps]
Kyon.
I've gotta favor to ask of you.
[KYON] After a couple of false
starts, Miss Asahina finally
started putting her words
into complete sentences
and began to explain.
[MIKURU] You might not believe
a word I'm about to say,
but the truth is, I'm not
actually from this time plane.
I come from the future.
I can't tell you from which
time period or time plane
I come from, though.
Telling anything about the
future to anyone from the past
is restricted.
I was told this before
I boarded the time machine.
Ah... think of it as being
a lot like animation.
The pictures look like
they're in motion, right?
But it's just a series of still
frames laid out in a sequence.
Time is just like that...
Time travelling is moving in a
three-dimensional direction
along the various time planes.
I'm from the future.
That means on this time plane,
I'm sort of like an extra
picture in the middle
of one of those flip book
animation things.
[KYON]
What is it now?
As for me, I'm here because
a large time click
happened three years ago.
That's three years ago from
the current time in this plane.
We arrived in the
past to investigate,
and we were surprised
once we got here.
No matter how hard we tried,
we couldn't go further back
in time from that plane.
The conclusion was that there
had to be a large time gap
between the time planes.
It wasn't until recently that we
found the thing that caused it.
That is... recently in the
future where I come from.
So what is the reason?
Miss Suzumiya.
[KYON]
Not again.
She was at the very center
of the time distortion,
and I can't explain any more
of this to you because
it's classified information.
But we are certain that it was
Miss Suzumiya who closed
our access to the past.
[KYON] It's hard to believe
that Haruhi would be able
to do something like that.
Believe me, it's a
mystery to us as well.
And Miss Suzumiya doesn't
realize that she's
the cause of the time quake,
either. That's where I come in.
I was sent here to see whether
or not there'll be any new
time anomalies occurring
near Miss Suzumiya.
I guess... I'm kind
of like a watchdog.
I'll understand if you
don't wanna believe
what I just told you.
No, it's not that, it's just...
why are you telling me?
Because you are the one that
Miss Suzumiya has chosen.
I can't explain because it's
classified information,
but you are very important
to Miss Suzumiya.
There are reasons behind
everything she does.
Every time she raises her
hand or takes a step.
What about Nagato
and the new guy?
[MIKURU] Oh, well, they're in
very similar positions to me.
I never expected Miss Suzumiya
to get us all together
in such a precise
manner, though.
So that means you
know who or what
both of them really are, right?
That's classified.
[gasps]
Can you tell me what's
going to happen to Haruhi?
[MIKURU]
That's classified.
Well, if you're
from the future,
you already know
what happens, right?
[MIKURU]
That's classified.
Well, then, why don't you just
tell Haruhi all this stuff?
[MIKURU]
That's classified.
I'm sorry, but I'm
not authorized
to say anything
right now.
You don't have to believe me.
I just wanted you to know
about it, that's all.
[KYON] I just heard the same
thing a couple of days ago,
didn't I?
[MIKURU] I'm sorry to dump
all this on you like I did.
Don't apologize, I don't mind.
[KYON] So now we've got an
alien and a time traveler.
What's going on here?
If there's anybody out there
who believes in all this stuff,
please, call me.
We'll trade places.
Miss Asahina.
Yes?
You mind if we put
all this on hold?
I mean, is it okay if we
just put aside whether
I believe you or not and
just get back to it later?
Sure.
Before we do, can I
ask you one question?
Yes, what is it?
If you wouldn't mind, could you
tell me how old you really are?
That's classified.
[KYON]
After that little conversation,
Haruhi called me on my cell,
and we all got together
again at noon.
Find anything?
[KYON]
Nothing.
Were you guys really looking?
I hope you weren't just
wandering around, Mikuru.
Ah! N-No!
What about you?
Did you find anything?
[KYON] While we ate lunch,
Haruhi said she wanted
to split up into groups again.
An unmarked one again.
[HARUHI] We'll meet back
at the station at four.
Make sure to find something
this time, you got that?
[KYON] This time, we split
up to search the north end
and the south end. Nagato
and me took the south side.
You know what you told me
about the other day?
What?
Well, suddenly I find
myself thinking that it
doesn't really sound so
far-fetched anymore.
Oh...
[KYON] If I have to pass
the time with Nagato,
this is about the
only place to do it.
[KYON]
Oh brother.
[screams]
[HARUHI] What time do you
think it is you idiot?!
[KYON] Sorry, but I
actually just woke up.
[HARUHI]
Huh?!
What did you just say to me?!
We were supposed to meet
you at four, right?
[HARUHI] Get your butt back
here! You got 30 seconds!
[KYON]
I had my work cut out for me.
We had to leave,
but getting Nagato to
move when she's reading
is impossible. First, I had
to get her a library card
so she could check out the book.
Meanwhile, I had to ignore the
incessant calls from Haruhi.
Late! Penalty!
[KYON] In the end, we
didn't find anything
even remotely close
to phenomena.
The day's activities
were a waste of both
my time and my money.
Before we split up though,
Miss Asahina...
I wanted to thank you for
listening to my story today.
[KYON] ...whispered into my ear,
which felt pretty good
if I may say so.
All right, spit it out, what
were you doing today?
Wait a minute, what about you?
Were you able to find any of
your mysterious phenomena today?
Well, they wouldn't be
careless enough to let you
find them in one day, right?
I mean, what did
you expect, anyway?
We're gonna need to review
your behavior on Monday.
[KYON]
And with that, she stormed off.
[sighs]
[KYON]
You're kidding me...
[KYON] The weekend was over,
and I was sweating from all
the humidity this morning.
Oh, the rainy season.
Haruhi walked in right
before the final bell rang.
Send me some of that breeze.
You're on your own there.
[sighs]
Hey, Suzumiya, ever happen
to hear the story
about the blue bird
of happiness?
What about it?
Nevermind, it doesn't have
to do with anything.
Then don't talk about it.
[KYON] After being showered from
behind by Haruhi's aura of
unpleasantness all day, I fled
to the safety of the club room.
Much like a rat running
from a brush fire...
There was someone
I needed to talk to.
Koizumi, don't you also have
something you want to
talk to me about
regarding Suzumiya?
Heh...
[KOIZUMI] I get the feeling that
the other two have already
talked to you about her,
am I right?
Yeah.
[KOIZUMI]
Well, how much do you know?
[KYON] Just that Suzumiya
isn't your ordinary person.
[KOIZUMI] Good. That'll make
my side of things easier,
because that's
definitely the case.
How about you start by telling
me who you really are?
Well, as you might've
already guessed,
I'm what's called an ESPer.
It's best we call it
that for now, okay?
To tell you the truth, I wasn't
planning on transferring
into this school so suddenly,
but the circumstances
have changed.
And I have to say that
I really didn't expect
the two of them to join up with
Haruhi Suzumiya so quickly.
Either way, I'm sure we're going
to have the chance to talk more
about all this later. A
picture's worth a thousand words
they say, and I definitely have
something to show you.
But for now, I think I'll give
you the short version.
The organization that
I belong to has
other ESPers besides yours
truly. Actually, this school's
already been secretly
infiltrated
by a bunch of us agents.
And ever since the organization
started up three years ago,
we've been watching
over Miss Suzumiya.
Three years ago.
That's when something
very interesting happened.
That is also when the powers I
have now awakened inside me.
How is Haruhi involved
in whatever happened
three years ago?
[KOIZUMI] You see, the elders
in the organization believe that
this world is sort
of like a dream that
a certain entity is showing us.
Because it's all just a dream,
it'd be quite easy for that
entity to alter our reality.
It could change it, destroy it,
even create a new world.
And we're pretty sure that we
found that entity right here.
You're saying that's Haruhi?
For millennia, people have
referred to such an entity
as "god" or something similar.
[KYON]
Well done, Haruhi.
You got people calling
you a god now.
Just look at this way for a
moment: you got ESPers like me
as well as beings like Mikuru
Asahina and Yuki Nagato
all hangin' around in the
same place. You think it's
simply coincidence that we've
all come together like this?
It's all happening because
Miss Suzumiya wished it.
She wished for it
three years ago.
So are you saying
that Haruhi remodeled
the universe three years ago?
Well, it would be more
accurate to say that
this world started
three years ago.
It's better than saying
it was remodeled.
Anyway, it's just a theory
us ESPers have.
Uh...
Whatever...
And just what do you ESPer
guys wanna do with Haruhi?
[KOIZUMI] Listen, if this
world upsets its god,
it'd be destroyed and recreated
in a blink of an eye.
We wanna prevent that
from happening.
I mean, I kinda like this place.
Warts and all, you know?
[KYON] Why don't you
just walk up to Haruhi
and talk to her about it?
Well, there are some members
in the organization who think
we should do just that, and
others think that we should be
more aggressive in
stimulating her powers.
Either way, most of us
think that this is
definitely not something that
we can easily get involved with.
The bottom line is that
she doesn't yet realize
her true potential.
If that's the case,
the organization feels
it'd be best if she
never finds out about her powers
and lives happily ever after.
You're gonna let
sleeping gods lie, huh?
Good way of putting it.
[KYON] You sure you guys aren't
the ones dreaming this world up?
I guess that's also
a possibility.
But as of right here, right now,
we're simply acting on
the worst of worst
case scenarios
that we can come up with.
I got an idea.
You're telling me you're
an ESPer, right?
If that's really the case,
then show me your power.
If you can do that,
then I'll believe
everything you've said
to me. For starters,
how 'bout you try heating up
this cup of coffee here?
While that would be
rather convenient,
my powers aren't like that.
In fact, most of the time, I
don't have any powers at all.
It's only when all sorts of
conditions are present
that I can actually use them.
And like I said
before, I believe
I'll have the opportunity to
show you in the near future.
I do apologize for speaking
for such a long time.
Now, excuse me. I think
that's enough for today.
See ya tomorrow.
[KOIZUMI]
Oh, by the way.
The biggest mystery
is definitely you.
I know it's kind of rude, but I
did some checking up on you.
I hope you don't mind it.
I assure you that you...
are an ordinary human.
[MIKURU]
Huh...?
[gasps]
[KYON gasps]
Uh! I'm so sorry about that!
Heh...
[KYON] Jeez, you don't
have to do everything
Haruhi tells you to do.
[KYON slurps]
[KYON]
For some reason,
Haruhi never showed up
to the clubroom that day.