[OKABE]
Uh, this is the place?
Are you sure?
Seems odd.
[MAHO]
I followed the directions.
Although I've never
been here before,
so who knows really?
[music playing]
[gasps]
[text notification]
Just got a message that
they're watching us.
"Enter by the maid uniform.
The one to your right."
[MAHO]
It's like a secret passageway.
This must be it.
[OKABE grunts]
Daru?!
What are you doing here?
Um, I'm pretty sure
you just stole my line, buddy.
[OKABE] I can't believe
you've been the one
analyzing the laptop.
[DARU]
And I can't believe
Mini Maho's the one
who hired me!
I gotta say, I never
saw that one coming.
[MAHO]
I'm getting really tired
of having to ask you
not to call me that.
Do you have any clue
how demeaning it is?
[DARU] Really?
But I think it's so cute!
Anyway, I'm kinda
pissed at you guys
for blowing the cover
off my part-time gig.
I had no idea
you did this job on the side.
Is that it?
[DARU]
Yeah. Imagine my shock
when I booted that bastard up
and saw her name.
I mean, Makise Kurisu's
personal laptop?
[OKABE] So, you two have been
in contact this entire time
without any knowledge
of the other's identity?
[MAHO]
I only knew I was talking
to a trustworthy
computer guru
who did data analysis
on the side.
And that they had a rule
never to meet face-to-face.
I gotta stay safe, doll.
Although I did suspect
it might be you
as soon as I checked out
the computer.
[OKABE]
Have you finished?
--Did you make it in?
--[DARU] Not yet.
Should take about
three more days.
Then abort it.
Do it right now!
--[MAHO gasps]
--[DARU] What?
Are you serious?
[OKABE growls]
Contained within that machine
is destructive,
malevolent information.
Data with the potential
to bring all of humanity
to ruin!
Delusional.
So lame!
What? Shut up!
No joke!
And it jeopardizes
Suzuha's safety!
--[DARU] Suzuha?
--Yes, her!
You should be aware of that!
If a time machine is--
Never mind.
[MAHO sighs]
I see.
You don't want to talk
about it in front of me, right?
I'm sorry.
[MAHO]
I get it.
I should probably leave then,
shouldn't I?
Come get me
when you're done.
[door creaks, clacks]
Okarin.
Don't you think it would
be better to just tell her?
[OKABE]
I can't.
You really don't want her
to know, huh?
[OKABE]
I do.
It's just...
if I tell Hiyajo
she might be, you know.
♪
Time machine?
I think this all
stems from that.
They want any trace
of her research,
and my guess is
her theories are in Amadeus.
So, they hacked it.
Because I'm...
I'm the one who--
--[MAHO sighs]
--[door creaks]
Huh?
All done?
No, um, actually.
I've decided that you deserve
to hear the whole story.
You sure?
Yeah.
I think it's unfair
to continue
to keep you in the dark.
But before I tell you,
promise me this.
[MAHO]
Hmm?
You won't try to save her,
no matter what!
Tell me you won't
even consider it!
[gasps]
[MAYURI] Okarin says that
something urgent came up,
so he won't be able to make it.
Well, that's too bad.
[MAYURI]
Yeah.
We talked about getting dinner
with everyone if he was able to,
but I guess he doesn't
have time after all.
Hmm?
♪
[RUKA]
Hey, Kagari?
You really like that
commercial, don't you?
Oh, I do.
[TV ANNOUNCER] Clear Kouhi!
With 50% less sugar!
Look for it in stores now!
♪
[MAHO]
No way!
[OKABE] Yeah. I don't
blame you for being skeptical.
I wouldn't
call it skepticism.
It's just mind boggling.
It's one thing in theory.
But you created a working
time machine?
[OKABE] A working time machine
is still a ways off.
What we created
is different.
We devised the Phone Wave,
which allowed us to send
what we called D-mails
into the past
to alter the present.
Then there's
the time leap machine.
[MAHO]
That's close enough in my book.
The method's irrelevant.
The result is what matters,
and you were able
to manipulate the past.
[MAHO]
As for the real time machine,
the fact that Suzuha's
here in the first place
means it exists somewhere,
isn't that right?
And what if it does?
[MAHO]
Huh?
Then that would mean...
Is this the reason
you ordered me
not to save Kurisu?
Yes. The past cannot be,
or rather, it must not be
manipulated by man.
I mean, never!
Yeah, but if we could
save Kurisu somehow,
we could avoid this situation.
[OKABE] I told you,
it's not that simple!
When you change the past,
everything you know
about the present and future
gets thrown out the window!
You might rob
the people you love
of their joy and success.
You could even strip the planet
of their very existence
without even realizing
what you were doing!
[MAHO]
You're lying.
[OKABE]
It's true.
What if the wrong people
get their hands on that laptop?
The powers that be would do
just about anything to have it.
It's a fearsome weapon,
maybe the most
formidable one ever made.
Do you understand?
We must eliminate the chance
that anyone
could use it for evil.
[MAHO] Don't you want
to see what's on her laptop?
[OKABE] Its mere existence
is enough to spark a global war,
so I'm fine
with not seeing it.
People will die,
and nothing will save them.
Still, it's proof
of Kurisu's life and work.
Her only legacy.
[OKABE] And if you
make one wrong move,
you could disgrace
that legacy,
you'd be trampling her memory.
No! That's not my intent,
you know that!
[OKABE]
Yes, I do.
But it doesn't matter.
You cannot deny
that's the risk you'd be taking
if you proceeded!
So, what do ya say?
[MAHO whimpers]
I understand.
So, let's destroy
this computer.
Thank you, Hiyajo.
[DARU]
Seriously?
What about getting
paid for my work?
'Cause I already
preordered a new hentai
that's coming out
at the end of the month
and can't return it.
You're truly despicable.
--[DARU] What?
--[computer beeping]
Who dares interrupt our
very important payment talk?
[OKABE]
It's them!
[MAHO]
What?
How could they have
tracked us down already?
-[phone vibrating]
-[DARU] Hmm?
Okey-dokey.
Abandon ship.
--You two make a run for it.
--[keyboard clacking]
But where can we go?
[OKABE]
They're already in the store!
Quiet, or they'll hear you.
[gasping]
This way.
[OKABE] I can't believe
it's come down to this.
Me, either, and that was one
of my favorite hideouts, too!
[grunting]
[DARU groans]
[DARU grunts]
[OKABE]
Where are we?
[DARU] Behind the last
building on the block.
We made it this far.
[MAHO yelps]
Leave her alone!
[VOICE (distorted)]
Do exactly as I say.
[whimpering]
Wait.
This is what
you're after, right?
Start by letting her go.
[VOICE (distorted)]
We'll trade you for her.
[MAHO] No! Don't give it
to them, Okabe!
Whatever you do,
do not fight back!
It's futile, you'll just
make things worse.
They're not bluffing.
They won't hesitate to kill you.
[MAHO]
But--
This computer is so
unbelievably secure,
the best hackers in the world
have tried for weeks
to crack it, without success.
And if you hurt her in any way,
I will make sure that you
never know what's on it.
[VOICE (distorted)]
Why should we believe you?
It's your choice.
[OKABE] If you let her go,
I'll hand it over.
You guarantee that all
three of us will be safe,
and I'll give you
the password.
[OKABE]
The world line hasn't changed.
In other words,
Daru and I
can't die right now.
In which case...
I can tell that
you don't trust me.
So release the girl,
and I'll agree
to be your hostage.
No, Okabe, don't.
Well, then?
[grunts]
Let her go and it's yours.
[MAHO yelps]
[tires screeching]
Get down!
[whines]
[gunfire stops]
[gunshot]
[tires squeal]
[whimpers]
[whines]
-[MAHO whimpers]
-[sirens wailing]
[REPORTER]
Residents of Akihabara
reported possible gunfire
to city police,
and upon further
investigation, their--
Are you sure
you're okay, Hiyajo?
Yeah, but we should
go to the hospital.
You need a doctor.
[OKABE] Doctors would
ask too many questions.
And besides...
Let me look at your hand.
What? Oh.
That's weird.
I can't open it.
It feels stuck.
[OKABE]
Her laptop.
You kept a piece?
I don't remember that.
[MAHO whispering]
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
But it's all my fault.
I failed her.
[crying]
I couldn't protect it.
[sobbing]
Forgive me...
I know I let you down, Kurisu.
I'm sorry!
I failed.
[sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
[FARIS] Are you sure
you're okay, meow?
[OKABE] Yeah.
Stopped bleeding, at least.
Where'd Daru-meow go?
He's laying low in one
of his other hideouts for now.
Said he needed
to give his work buddies
a quiet heads up.
Did you want this?
Yes, we still need
to disinfect your wound,
'cause you never know.
That kit should have
alcohol swabs and bandages.
[OKABE]
I knew things were different.
In this world line,
SERN and the Rounders
have no part
in what's unfolded.
Which means...
Based on Braun's hunch
that it's America,
it must be DURPA or Stratfor.
So, the Russians came
and opened fire.
[FARIS] Maho-meow sure is
taking her time.
Maybe we should
go check on her.
[MAHO]
Time travel.
I still can't believe it.
What the--?
[groaning]
I can't-- Oh, no!
Something about the shift
from tension to relaxation
has caused all
my muscles to go limp!
--[knocking]
--[FARIS] Maho-meow!
Hi! Oh my goodness,
what's the matter with you?!
--[MAHO] Faris!
--Oh no, meow!
Maho's dying!
We have to save her, meow!
We have to do something!
It's gonna be okay!
--We just have to hurry--
--[MAHO] Stop it!
You'll expose me!
What's going--
[FARIS gasping]
[MAHO wails]
Faris, my towel!
[screams]
--[OKABE] I'm so embarrassed.
--[MAHO] Me, too.
It wasn't your fault, though,
so don't worry
about it too much.
But, like, will you swear
to forget what you saw?
[OKABE]
I'll do my best.
When someone asks you that,
you're supposed to just
tell them you will.
Otherwise you're in danger.
I'll stab an electrode
in your hippocampus.
--[gasps]
--Huh?
[chuckles]
I take it Kurisu sang
her little rhyme to you, too?
[MAHO] She made me promise
not to tell the professors
something bad
she said about them.
I could absolutely
see that one happening.
[MAHO]
They were all scared of her.
I kinda thought she'd snap
and do it for real someday.
[OKABE sighs]
[OKABE]
I'm gonna go now.
You should regain
muscle function soon.
Until then,
you'd better sleep.
Okay.
Night.
--[MAHO] Okabe?
--Huh?
Would you mind
if I asked you
to stay with me
a little longer?
A few minutes?
[OKABE]
I'll stay until you fall asleep.
Just try to get some rest.
Sorry for being a pain.
[OKABE]
No.
What you went through today
is enough to rattle anyone.
You're not a pain at all.
Yeah, you've got a good point.
I've been wondering.
Was Salieri relieved
or did he have regrets...
...when he found out
Mozart died?
[OKABE]
I don't know.
You warned me
before it all went down
about disgracing the dead.
When you said that,
it made me realize.
Maybe I had already
disgraced her.
After she died,
I acquired her computer.
I told myself
that it was her will,
that Kurisu would
have wanted it.
I vowed to carry on
her legacy.
I thought I should be the one
to bear the torch for her.
--[keyboard clacking]
--And yet...
[keyboard clacking]
[MAHO]
In that moment,
I realized it was
only frustration.
I wanted to crack it.
To prove that I could
see what it held.
I needed to know
that I... could.
[OKABE]
So it became your obsession?
It felt that way.
There was a part of me
that just wanted to break in.
To find the secrets she hid,
to know her truth.
That's all.
[OKABE]
Not buying it.
It's true.
Think about it.
Mozart didn't waste a second
fretting over Salieri.
He devoted his life
to making music,
and that was it.
[OKABE]
Hiyajo, listen.
In the end, you were willing
to destroy the computer.
That's because
you were in danger.
[OKABE]
No, it isn't just that.
You were devastated
that you weren't able
to protect her legacy
like you wanted to.
That's the truth.
And I think,
that alone is proof enough
of what you hold in your heart.
[MAHO]
You give me too much credit!
You don't know.
Look at it this way.
If what you say is true,
you wouldn't have
held onto that piece
of her computer
like you did.
At least, that's what I think.
[gasps]
Uh, you seem
to have recovered.
If I stay, you won't
be able to sleep,
so I should probably go.
Just shout if
you need anything.
--[MAHO] Hey.
--[OKABE] Hmm?
[MAHO]
After you and Kurisu
finished the time leap machine,
you were forced
to repeat the same interval
over and over again,
weren't you?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
And were you and Kurisu...?
[MAHO] Never mind.
Don't answer that.
Hope you have a nice night.
[OKABE]
Same to you.
[door clicks]
[ALEXIS]
Maho!
Whatever will you do
without Rintaro?
[MAHO] You're choking me.
I can't breathe!
--[ALEXIS laughs]
--[MAHO] Stop it!
I'm dying, for real!
Thank you for coming
to see us off, Rintaro,
and everybody else
from your little lab.
By the way, when do you
plan to come to our lab
and start working
with us, buddy?
[OKABE]
Wait, are-- are you--
The professor's been
saying he won't rest
until you come to
Viktor Chondria University.
And he means it.
--[OKABE] Why me?
--I'd never forgive myself
if I let the young
Japanese Einstein
slip right through my fingers!
Love to have you
on the team, Rintaro.
Well, then, I'll study hard
and do my best to get accepted.
--You okay?
--Huh?
Yep! If that's where Okarin
wants to go to school,
then of course
I'm all for it!
[KAEDE gasps] What happened
to your hand, Yuki?
[laughing]
Oh, I just nicked myself
with a knife at work.
Want me to carry that? Or, um--
[YUKI giggles]
Sure! You're sweet.
What about Suzuha?
Well, uh, she's still
struggling to accept the truth.
Now that Kurisu's
computer's been destroyed,
we can rest assured
the conflict between Russia
and America won't take place.
You might be correct,
but it still doesn't
eliminate all possibility
of World War III.
[MAHO]
What next?
[OKABE] I've done
everything in my power
for the time being,
but you don't need
to worry about it.
[ALEXIS] Are you two planning
a future date over here?
Would you give it
a rest for once?
That reminds me.
I hate to say it,
but this means
we're gonna have to revoke
Rintaro's access to Amadeus.
Too bad. Would you like to say
goodbye to her one last time?
Yes, I would.
Don't worry,
I'll make it quick.
-[phone chimes]
-What's up?
I just wanted to tell you
goodbye, is all.
[AMADEUS] Have you said
goodbye to Miss Maho yet?
-'Cause you should!
-Sure did!
Oh. Then I guess it's all right.
How many times is it
that I've had
to bid you farewell?
-Feels so--
-What?
[OKABE]
Nothing. N-Never mind.
Well, I suppose I'm grateful
you took the time
to talk to me.
I hear you might be coming
to study with us, right?
I guess I'll try
to remember you
until we meet again.
[chuckles]
What a tsundere.
Hey! I mean, what?
[OKABE]
Your face has gone crimson.
Kurisu's quite the shy one!
[laughs]
Time to go, Professor.
Oh, yes, of course.
One thing.
Promise you won't
tease Hiyajo too much?
[AMADEUS]
I can't promise that.
See you.
--[AMADEUS] Okabe?
--Huh?
Someday, I hope you
remember how to laugh
from the bottom
of your heart.
Bye, now.
♪
[MAHO]
Okabe?
Thank you for everything.
Especially for saving my life.
That's quite a stretch.
No, it's what happened,
and I'm incredibly grateful.
See you soon
in the States!
[OKABE] And so,
with goodbyes exchanged,
Professor Leskinen and Hiyajo
returned to America.
Time marches on once more.
Without anything changing,
and without repeating,
it moves as it should.