[MOEKA]
I got your message.
I'm Moeka Kiryu.
[OKABE gasping]
[MOEKA]
Can I come in?
[DARU]
You made it!
What's your problem, Okarin?
Let the pretty lady in.
Oh, yes.
[SUZUHA]
Here, have some tea.
[OKABE]
Moeka Kiryu.
Why is she here?
How do she and Daru--?
[NEWS MAN 01A]
None of which were human.
The carcasses, later discovered
to be orangutan and chimpanzee,
were found with their brains
and sections of their
craniums missing.
--[toy gun beeping]
--Huh?
What's wrong?
[OKABE gasps]
Nothing.
[OKABE]
Remain calm.
We aren't in that
world line anymore.
In this one, there's nothing
to alert SERN to us.
Moeka has no reason
to kill Mayuri.
She won't kill Mayuri.
She won't kill May--
[SUZUHA]
Uncle?
You don't look so hot.
I'm fine, thanks.
Daru, care to explain?
Who is this woman?
Miss Kiryu.
She's a local
freelance journalist.
That's right.
Here's my card.
[DARU] A while back,
some magazine was doing
a fluff piece on the
urban legends of Akiba.
She got in touch
'cause she wanted
to schedule an
interview with me
about my part-time work, so...
Your work?
[DARU] You know,
the stuff I can't mention,
but that I hint about,
all mysterious-like?
I'm always really careful
not to leave any traces,
but somehow, Moeka still managed
to track me down. She's wily.
So, then, that explains
your interest in her.
I'd like to help.
Your friend's missing?
Kinda. We're actually on
the hunt for a little girl
who went missing in
Akihabara 12 years ago.
[MOEKA]
In 1998.
Yep.
The girl's name
is Kagari Shiina.
She was 10 years old
back when she disappeared,
which would mean
that she's 22 today.
Obviously.
She's alive?
Well, we don't know
that for sure.
But we found a picture
on the interwebs
that sorta resembles her.
[OKABE] Should we be
trusting this woman?
She could have ulterior motives.
But there's no reason for her
to seek us out in
this world line,
and she has no reason
to kill Mayuri.
Even so, it's more
likely than not
she's a Rounder
in this line, too.
The killer's instinct
is still there.
Uh...
[OKABE gasps]
If you'll let me, I'll help.
Yeah?
Yes, but I can't promise
you I'll find her.
Right. It is a tough
assignment, for sure.
We'll compensate you
upon completion,
but we'll also cover any
expenses you might rack up
while on the job.
No problem.
Does all that work
for you, Okarin?
Um, sure.
[DARU] Great! Well, I guess
you're officially hired.
[BRAUN]
Let's go, Nae.
[NAE]
'Kay!
[BRAUN]
All right!
Don't forget your seatbelt.
[NAE]
Got it!
[engine starts]
You ready?
[NAE]
Mm-hmm.
Off we go!
[BRAUN]
[NAE giggles]
[SUZUHA]
So, that woman.
Huh?
[SUZUHA] You know her from
somewhere else, don't you?
Huh?
Why would you make
that assumption?
It was so obvious.
Wait, you know her?
I don't. You're wrong.
Not even in the
alpha world line?
[gasps]
[SUZUHA sighs]
All right.
You clearly don't want to say.
Just know that I'm going
to be on guard around her.
Fine with me, for now.
What's up with you?
Just my general unease.
Aha! She plays into your
--[phone buzzing]
--Barbara Gordon fantasies
--which I totally get
because I'm on board with the
whole "hot librarian" fetish.
[MAHO sighs]
[MAHO] I should probably get a
professional to help with this.
[MAHO sighs]
[AMADEUS]
It's strange.
No matter how much I call him,
he never answers anymore.
What's going on?
Why is he even a tester?
Maybe his phone is
broken. Occam's razor.
I guess. Hopefully,
that's all it is.
[MAHO] Because Makise
Kurisu was murdered.
Now this is something
I never thought I'd witness.
--Maho? Brooding?
--[MAHO gasps]
[MAHO] Professor, how long
have you been standing there?
I just walked in.
These Japanese
convenience stores
sure put the ones
in America to shame.
You can get a different
bento box every single day.
Then the next week, there's
an entirely new selection!
You shouldn't eat
that stuff all the time.
You'll die young
of a heart attack.
[ALEXIS chuckles]
I refuse to be judged by the
reigning queen of cup-o-noodles.
[MAHO groans]
[ALEXIS]
So, where are you off to?
To Akihabara. I just
need a change of pace.
You don't have to lie.
I know you're going to
see Rintaro, and I approve.
[gasps] That's not why!
[ALEXIS]
You sure about that?
I guess I could swing
by the lab on the way.
"On the way"?
On the way to what?
That's absolutely
none of your business.
So you're willing to take an
hour-long trip to Akihabara
where Rintaro's lab
happens to be,
just so you can get
a little change of pace.
Am I understanding correctly?
Uh...
I support you.
Stop! I am going,
but it's not what you think!
It isn't at all like that!
[ALEXIS]
It's not like what, Maho?
I'm done being
interrogated, thank you!
Good bye!
[chuckles]
Tell Rintaro "hi" for me.
[papers rustling]
[OKABE]
What is this?
[MOEKA]
My report.
[SUZUHA]
So?
[OKABE] Finding her might
be even more difficult
than we thought.
That's not good.
[gasps]
What's up? Did you find a clue?
Not quite. Just something
that might be of interest.
Let me see.
Uh--hey!
"While investigating,
I made a strange discovery
pertaining to the case.
Over the course
of several months,
another party has been
searching for Kagari Shiina
in addition to our own,
or so the evidence
would suggest."
What does that mean?
Just what it states.
[DARU]
Who else is looking for her?
That I don't know.
Suzuha's been searching.
Maybe it's her.
[SUZUHA]
That was my first thought, too.
But look, check this out.
The search party
was composed of men,
and there was a
foreigner among them.
[SUZUHA]
A foreigner?
Well, Kagari's been
gone for 12 years.
Perhaps she made friends
who are searching now, too.
[DARU] Yeah, a 10-year-old
wouldn't have survived long
without an adult taking
care of her in some way.
I mean, hypothetically.
This new evidence does
support one theory, though.
Which is?
[OKABE]
It raises the likelihood
that Kagari Shiina
is currently alive.
But who is this foreigner?
I'm pretty sure
the lab was this way.
[MAHO]
Hey. I'm in Akihabara,
so I thought that I would
swing by the lab. Period.
That is, if you happen
to be there. Period.
[gasps]
[MAHO gasping, panting]
[MAHO panting]
[MAN 05A gasps]
[ALL]
Huh?
[MAHO panting]
[clattering]
[gasps]
[MAHO panting]
[MAHO]
Come on! Please answer!
Hello? Okabe?
[OKABE]
Hiyajo?
[MAHO]
Yeah, it's me!
I'm running toward the lab,
but someone's--[gasps]
--[dial tone]
--What's going on?
--Hey, Hiyajo!
[DARU]
Okarin?
[OKABE]
Hiyajo!
Huh?
[OKABE]
It can't be.
Please don't let it be that.
[OKABE]
It's not happening! Not again!
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
Hiyajo! Huh?
Wait. What--?
[MAHO]
Get away! Just back off!
[OKABE]
What are you doing?
You villain! Unhand her!
[MAHO gasps]
Okabe, stop!
[REYES gasps]
[REYES]
Are you Maho's boyfriend?
Well, uh, not quite.
[gasps]
[OKABE]
Whoa! What is this?
Hiyajo! Why--?
You see?
I said to back off, didn't I?
[REYES]
I'm Judy Reyes!
[OKABE]
Reyes?
[MAHO]
Professor Judy Reyes.
She's here in Japan
for an AI conference.
She snuck up on
me in an alley.
Not weird at all, Judy.
Professor?
At Viktor Chondria University?
[REYES]
That's right!
[gasps]
[OKABE chuckles]
It's lovely to meet you.
I'm sorry for the yelling.
[REYES laughs]
It's fine. I enjoyed it.
Uh...
Anyway.
You must be Rintaro.
Alexis told me about you.
[OKABE]
Alexis?
Oh, Professor Leskinen.
[MAHO] Ms. Reyes' specialty
is psychophysiology.
Right. The mind-body link.
I study how cognitive
processes manifest physically.
In the organs,
pathology, et cetera.
Yeah, it's kind of heroic.
That field is much more
important to humanity
than what Leskinen
and I are doing.
Your work is more useful.
[REYES] That's not true at all.
Amadeus is remarkable.
It might even prove
to be highly beneficial.
I sure hope you're right.
We'll see. Thanks.
So, um, why did you stalk me
all the way from the station
into this dark alley?
From the station? Stalk you?
What do you mean?
Wait. Weren't you following me?
I was just walking by and
saw you standing here.
I thought I'd jump out
and surprise you.
But then...
[MAHO]
Did I... imagine it?
Anyway, you and your
boyfriend come visit me soon.
We can talk more. Bye!
Hang on!
You're wrong!
He is not my boyfriend!
Okay, what was that?
[MAHO]
Uh--please. Let's forget this.
[DARU]
Okarin!
[MAHO]
Huh?
You guys okay?
Yeah. It was just a false alarm.
Oh, hey! Miss Hiyajo, it's you!
[DARU humming]
Is it me, or have you
gotten even tinier
since the last time
I saw you? Well?
[MAHO] Are you dumb enough
to think that's possible?
[DARU squeals]
[DARU] She's a feisty one,
just how I like 'em!
Does Hiyajo's presence indicate
that she's going to be
inducted into the lab as our
token Legal Loli member?
Very doubtful.
Well, nonetheless!
You get a nickname!
You're Mini Maho!
No, thank you.
Really.
[OKABE]
Amadeus did?
[MAHO]
That's right.
She said you won't
answer her calls,
like you're blowing
her off or something.
[MAHO] And judging by
the look on your face,
I'd say she was
right on the money.
[OKABE]
Well...
Uh--
[MAHO] Let me talk to
the professor about this.
[MAHO] It was only
supposed to be a test.
You're not obligated to help.
We're not even paying you.
I can't.
I had no idea.
I guess Kurisu had a more
impactful presence in your life
than I assumed.
Look, we've been
over this already.
Kurisu wasn't--
[MAHO]
Don't insult me!
She had a huge effect on you.
And this isn't healthy.
You're projecting your
feelings onto Amadeus.
When you see her and you hear
her voice, you come alive.
I can sense your feelings
growing for her,
and it makes me afraid for you.
Because Amadeus is nothing more
than a system of algorithms.
Just memory and data.
It's not really her at all.
[OKABE]
I know that.
I do, I--
[OKABE]
And yet...
It's made of Kurisu's
memories, without a doubt!
Okabe...
[OKABE]
I know it's not her.
The real Kurisu is gone.
And what's in here is only
a model, but, still...
[OKABE]
I just can't.
Give me a little more time.
[MAYURI] Do you have
any plans for New Year's?
[OKABE]
Another party in the forecast?
[MAYURI] Mm-hmm! First,
we'll go visit the shrine,
then we'll have
a big New Year's meal
and share our hopes and
dreams for the year ahead!
I'm in. That sounds delightful.
Won't it be perfect?
I'll ask the others later
and see what they say.
Okay! I've gotta go out
and do a little shopping.
For ComiMa?
[MAYURI] Uh-huh! I need to
find a couple more accessories
for Fubuki's costume,
or it won't look right.
There's not much time
left to finish, huh?
[MAYURI]
Mm.
And when that's done,
the whole year is
pretty much over.
It passed in the
blink of an eye, huh?
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
"In the blink of an eye."
The fateful summer.
All those days and hours I lived
and relived, how many times?
And yet...
...the year still
comes to an end.
[MAYURI gasps, giggles]
[MAYURI giggling]
[MAYURI]
It's snowing!
You think it'll stick? [giggles]
[OKABE]
Time marches on...
...in this world line
that I chose.
[MAYURI]
Whoa! It's so magical!
Okarin! I'm gonna get going!
[OKABE]
Uh, bye.
[MAYURI]
Oh, that's right.
Ruka was looking
for you earlier.
You should pick up the phone
and call if you get a chance.
I completely forgot
Ruka called me.
I'll do that right now.
Okay! Say hi for me!
[ringing]
[OKABE]
Probably busy.
They've got their work
cut out for them,
readying the shrine
for New Year's crowds.
[knocking]
Huh?
[RUKA]
May I come in?
Rukako? Yes, it's open!
Oh, you're here! I'm glad!
Hi. I'm sorry,
is this about earlier?
I forgot all about it, but I
did just try to call you back.
[RUKA]
Huh? Wow! You did!
Well, sorry for not answering.
I didn't notice.
[OKABE chuckles]
No worries.
You said you needed
to speak with me?
[RUKA]
Uh, yeah.
But I'd prefer to show you.
Because, you see, there's
someone who I want you to meet.
I brought them along.
Is that all right?
[OKABE]
I must admit, I'm intrigued.
Uh...?
[OKABE]
Ku...
Kurisu.
[OKABE]
Here you go.
Thank you.
[OKABE]
They're so alike.
Except her voice is different.
What synchronicity.
What would Jung say?
So, Rukako, who is this?
Rukako?
Uh, sorry.
It's just a pet name.
On account of
Ruka's femininity.
I told you on the phone that
my father had house guests,
and that they'd be
staying a while.
[gasps] And this is that guest?
[RUKA]
Yes, my father's acquaintance
brought her to the house, too.
What's your name?
[WOMAN gasps]
Actually, that brings me to
the main reason we came here.
[OKABE]
Hm?
Well, um...
Do you have any idea... how we
could find out who she is?
[OKABE]
What do you mean, exactly?
You see, she has severe amnesia.
[gasps]
[RUKA]
She doesn't remember anything.
Not her name,
or where she came from,
or even how she lost her memory.
It's all a blank to her.
You can't be serious.
[RUKA]
I immediately thought that
if anyone could help her
remember, it'd be you.
'Cause you know all
about those things--
brains, memory, difficult stuff.
Anything would help.
[RUKA gasps]
Anything!
Please, I need to remember!
Whoa, let's take
a step back here.
I spout off about this subject,
but I am no neuroscientist.
Besides, regaining memories
is never simple.
Storing them alone
is complicated.
Yes, of course.
Well, in that case,
can you think of some other way
for us to find out
who she might be?
Even if Kana can't remember?
[OKABE]
Kana? Where'd that come from?
Not having a name is annoying,
so we just call her Kana.
Father made it up.
[OKABE]
That's a nice one, I guess.
Not that it matters.
It's a placeholder
until I know more.
Can you help me?
[gasps]
[OKABE]
I can try.
Do you have any
clues to speak of?
Something like a wallet or a
cellphone, or even a bus pass?
No, I don't have anything.
[OKABE]
Well you made it this far.
There must be some
hint from your life
that you're overlooking.
There is one thing
that could be a lead.
It's from her past.
Do you have it?
Yes.
It's this.
--[door opens]
--[MAYURI] Too-too-roo!
Okarin, I'm back!
It stopped snowing. Boo.
Oh, hi.
We have a guest?
[KANA gasps]
One of these?
[MAYURI gasps]
An oopa!
Oh, wow, where did you
get this little guy?
It's Kana's.
I think she's always had it.
She takes it
everywhere she goes.
Interesting!
I'm pretty sure it was
green at some point.
I think this is the special
forest fairy edition!
A forest fairy, huh?
[MAYURI]
Mm!
It showed up in a movie
not too long ago.
You see? It's kinda
like the one I have,
but the design is
a little different.
That one has fairy wings!
Hold on.
Why does this one
seem to be ancient?
If the film came out--[gasps]
I'm back now! [gasps]
Kana?
Hey! Are you all right? Kana!
Kagari?
[ALL gasp]
[SUZUHA]
That's her! Kagari!
That's who we've
been looking for!