[MAYURI]
Kagari?
Wake up, sweetheart.
[MAYURI]
Rise and shine!
Mommy?
[MAYURI]
How are you feeling, love?
My treatment for today...
Is it over now?
[MAYURI] Yup!
And you did so well!
That's my girl!
[sighs]
[MAYURI] So I think
you've earned a big reward!
I have very special
news for you!
Special news?
[MAYURI]
Well, love, all the paperwork
has finally been processed,
and I'm sorry
it took so long.
But beginning today,
I'm officially
your real mommy
and your legal guardian!
Now we can
finally live together!
[gasps]
[big gasp]
[KAGARI]
Mommy! [laughs]
[MAYURI]
Sheesh!
You're getting to be
so strong, Kagari!
[KAGARI laughs]
[MAYURI] ♪ Searching for
just one little thing. ♪
♪ The laughter
hiding in the stars. ♪
What is that song, Mommy?
[MAYURI]
Hmm?
I'm so glad you asked.
It's a very precious
song to me.
Oh, really?
[MAYURI]
That's right!
It means the world to me,
you know why?
Because I was only
able to meet you
thanks to that song.
--[KAGARI] Oh, that's nice.
--[MAYURI] Yep!
And now you're old enough
to learn it, too,
so I'll start teaching you
how it goes.
Maybe someday you'll meet
someone you hold dear,
and then you'll be able
to share it with them!
I want to learn it
and sing it, Mommy!
Teach me to sing
your precious song!
[MAYURI giggles]
Okay!
Now listen
and repeat after me.
Yeah!
[MAYURI] ♪ Searching for
just one little thing. ♪
[KAGARI] ♪ Searching for
[MAYURI giggles]
That was perfect, Kagari!
♪ The laughter hiding
in the stars. ♪
[KAGARI] ♪ The laughter
hiding in the stars. ♪
[MAYURI giggles]
♪ Shining like
oceans in the sun. ♪
[KAGARI]
♪ Shining like... ♪
[rain pattering]
[IZAKI]
Hey, Okabe!
Hello, Professor.
[IZAKI] I've been
meaning to tell you
that report you turned in
was pretty darn impressive!
Wow. Thanks,
I'm happy to hear it.
Didn't you tell me that you were
considering studying abroad?
[OKABE]
Well, yes, tentatively.
To be honest with you,
your performance had me
worried you couldn't cut it,
but with your
recent coursework,
I think you just
might pull it off!
Keep it up, Okabe.
Yes, I will!
Thanks for the support, sir!
[MAYURI]
Hey, Kagari!
You want some Juicy
Number One Chicken Tenders?
They're my favorite food
in the whole wide world!
[KAGARI]
You don't mind?
[MAYURI]
Of course not!
I love sharing them
with my friends.
Especially the ones who
have never had them before!
I'd love to try.
And thank you
so much for offering.
[MAYURI giggles] Well,
you are totally welcome.
So, what about you, Daru?
[DARU]
Sure, I'll have some.
[MAYURI]
Okay, sounds good!
Give me just
a few minutes.
[MAYURI] ♪ Searching for
just one little thing. ♪
♪ The laughter hiding
in the stars. ♪
♪ Shining like-- ♪
--Huh?
--[KAGARI] That song...
I know it.
[MAYURI]
What's the matter?
Huh?
Somewhere...
...so long ago,
I knew that song.
Are you okay?
--[MAYURI gasps]
--Ah! Oh, crap!
Kagari! Hang in there!
Can you hear me?
[door slams]
[OKABE pants]
Mayuri! How's Kagari?
--Okarin!
--[panting]
You said she collapsed again?
[SUZUHA] Yeah,
she's sleeping now.
Suzuha.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
[SUZUHA]
It's been quite a while.
[OKABE]
Yeah.
Just so we're clear,
I'm no longer--
[SUZUHA] You're no longer
trying to reach Steins Gate.
I can read you
like a book, Okabe.
[OKABE]
I accept that.
[SUZUHA] I wonder if
they'll ever come back.
[OKABE]
What?
[SUZUHA]
Kagari's memories.
[OKABE]
Right.
The fact still remains,
she's a war orphan.
She never knew
her parents' faces,
and I'm sure most of her
memories are traumatic.
But then,
she met Mayuri,
and her life changed.
She had a somewhat
normal childhood.
Because of Mayuri,
Kagari was able to smile,
maybe for the first time.
[SUZUHA] When Kagari
ran away from me
in the past, she held
me at gunpoint.
[gasps]
[SUZUHA] She said that
if the world line changed,
she might never meet
her Mommy Mayuri.
She was only
ten years old.
Her memories
might come back,
or maybe they won't.
But I do wonder,
which outcome would be
happier for her?
If her memory
does return,
it could help.
She might remember
the people who attacked her,
which could prove
to be quite helpful.
[SUZUHA]
Hmph.
Well, either way,
my intentions haven't changed.
I plan to do
everything in my power,
and I will not stop.
Take care of Kagari.
Promise me.
[MAYURI] ♪ Searching for
just one little thing. ♪
♪ The laughter ♪
--♪ hiding in the stars. ♪
-[KAGARI] Mommy? Mommy!
[MAYURI]
♪ Shining like-- ♪
[KAGARI]
Mommy!
[BOTH gasp]
[KAGARI gasps]
Sorry.
It just happened
again, didn't it?
[OKABE]
Are you all right?
Yes, thanks.
[OKABE] Mayuri stepped out
just a little while ago.
I guess they were
short staffed at May Queen.
They needed her
to come in for the lunch shift.
Mayushii has been worrying
herself sick over you, though.
That's so sad.
[faucet squeaks]
Do you feel
any better yet?
I heard a song
that I know.
And then, something odd
happened in my head.
A song?
Was it one that
you've heard before?
[KAGARI]
Yes.
[OKABE] But you
didn't hear it recently?
It's not new,
I don't think.
I see.
[DARU] What are you
thinking, Okarin?
[OKABE]
It's a good sign.
Could mean a lot of things,
like, your memories
might be coming back.
Do you believe that?
If it wouldn't be
too hard on you,
it's something we could
probably explore.
I think I would
be open to that.
I'm okay now.
[KAEDE]
So, how was your check-up?
[FUBUKI] Great! Turns out I'm
healthier than I've ever been.
It has been a full two weeks
for crying out loud!
I mean, you don't see
Okarin having to go in
for check-ups all the time.
So, why do I have to?
[BOTH laugh]
You should be grateful that
you don't have any real issues.
[FUBUKI]
But I do, I have major issues!
I put on a bunch of weight
when I was in the hospital.
And I can't get it
to come off!
[YUKI laughs]
Hey, what do you guys say
we go do some
karaoke after this?
Ah. Sorry, can't.
I have plans that
I don't wanna break.
Ah, shoot!
In fact, I've gotta hurry!
But I want to do
karaoke with you soon!
--[FUBUKI gasps]
--Yuki, watch out!
--[thud]
--[grunts]
[BOTH groan]
[YUKI]
Ouch!
[groans]
[FUBUKI] Jeez, I can't believe
how clumsy that girl is.
[KAEDE]
For real.
[MAYURI]
Hey, Kagari!
Are you feeling
better now?
[KAGARI] Yeah. And I'm really
sorry that I worried you.
[MAYURI]
Mm-mm.
[MAYURI] I'm the one
who needs to apologize.
I never should
have left your side!
--A song?
--That's right.
It's the one that
you were singing
in the lab earlier today.
I'm pretty sure I've heard it
somewhere before.
It would really help
if you could tell us
where you heard it.
Kagari thinks she knew it
before the amnesia.
Might be the key
to recovering her memories.
Um, let me see.
I first heard that song
from Suzuha,
but I'm not sure
where she learned it.
--From Suzuha?
--[MAYURI] Yep!
She used to
sit and sing it
while she stared
out the window,
and that happened
so much I memorized it.
But I don't know
what it's from,
or even the name of it,
so I'm not gonna be
much help here.
[OKABE]
Huh.
[OKABE] It could be a
popular song in the future.
Interesting.
[MAYURI] Sorry, I feel like
my answer was a letdown.
[KAGARI] Mm-mm. Thank you for
telling us what you do know.
Hey, Okarin?
Are you still planning
to visit Suzuha later?
Huh? Yeah, I was thinking
of going to check on her.
[MAYURI] Do you mind
if I come along with you?
Really?
You would do that?
[MAYURI]
Yeah, I would.
It's hard to explain,
but Kagari, when I see you,
it inspires me
to do anything
and everything
I can to help out!
So, then, please?
[KAGARI]
As long as you're sure.
But don't you still
have to work?
The rush is over,
so I think we'll survive
without her.
[OKABE]
Hmm, that's settled, then.
Guess I better give
Suzuha a heads up.
[line ringing]
She might be working.
If that were the case,
she'd be in the middle
of her lunch break now.
Oh, I passed her
on the street
right outside here
a little while ago.
Seriously?
[FARIS humming]
Hey, Suzu-meow!
Oh, it's just you, Rumi.
So, what's with the
scary-looking face, huh?
Because I'm--
I'm about to head into battle.
Into battle?
[FARIS] That was exactly
how she said it.
[OKABE gasps]
Don't tell me...
♪
[groaning]
[gags]
[CROWD murmuring]
[MEN groaning]
[fork clatters]
--[bell dinging]
--[CROWD gasping]
There you have it!
This month's
curry-eating contest winner
is our very first
three-time champ,
--The Silent Slaughterer!
--[CROWD applauds]
And to think,
I'm not even full yet.
[SUZUHA]
Eat all you can, when you can.
It's the most important rule
to live by on the battlefield.
[OKABE] You had me
worried for a moment.
[SUZUHA sighs]
How embarrassing.
I can't believe
you really heard me singing.
Don't be embarrassed,
it was adorable!
[SUZUHA] Please spare me
the flattery, Mayuri.
Do you have any memory
of where you heard
that song, Suzuha?
My mo-- I mean,
I heard Yuki singing it
once upon a time.
You heard it from Yuki?
When you say Yuki sang it,
do you mean that it
happened in the future?
Yeah. Mom had
this habit of singing
while she was
preparing meals.
So then, it's possible
that Kagari learned it
from either you or Yuki
before she lost her memory.
No, not possible.
Mayuri adopted Kagari
after my mom died,
so Kagari couldn't
have heard it from Mom.
And I'm totally certain
I never sang it
in front of Kagari, either.
[OKABE]
Kagari learned it from Mayuri,
Mayuri from Suzuha,
and Suzuha from Yuki.
This is just like
a game of "telephone."
[line ringing]
--[OKABE] No luck?
--No luck.
Maybe Yuki is working
or something
[OKABE]
Well, no matter.
We'll just have to wait
until she calls you back.
Sorry, it's strange, but look.
--[OKABE] Huh?
--[MAYURI] Hmm?
[MAYURI]
Hey! Yuki's right there!
[OKABE]
Wait. Is she sitting with...
...Daru?!
Aww!
Uh... [giggles]
You've got a
little bit of sauce
on the side
of your mouth, there.
[DARU gasps]
No! Wait!
I'll wipe it off myself!
--Please don't try to clean...
--You can't see where it is!
My disgusting face grease
is sure to ruin it forever!
[YUKI giggles]
It isn't disgusting at all.
[DARU gasps]
[MAYURI] Hey! Do you guys
think they're on a date?
I hope they are.
So those two are kind of
seeing each other? Wow.
That rascal.
Saying he just had
somewhere else to be.
[MAYURI]
What should we do, Okarin?
We should probably
avoid interrupting them.
Let's just check back in.
Is that okay
with you, Kagari?
Sure. Although...
Huh?
--[OKABE] Uh...
--[MAYURI] Hmm.
[KAGARI] We're really
sorry for intruding.
[YUKI]
Don't be!
Like the old saying goes,
the more the merrier!
[giggles]
Right?
[DARU chuckles sadly]
Yeah, cool, whatever.
So, what can you tell us
about the song?
Oh, you see, sometimes
on my days off,
I help teach a baking class
at the community center.
--Huh?
--Yuki's really talented!
She makes the best
sweets ever!
--[gasps]
--Oh!
Maybe you could
come bake with me
the next time I do it!
Yes, of course!
Hold on just a minute.
Sorry, I fail to see
what your class
has to do with the song.
One of the regular students
always comes in singing it.
That's where
I heard it the first time.
Wait, are you sure
it's the same one?
Yeah.
For some reason, it always
gets stuck in my head.
Is it possible that the person
who sang it knows any of us?
I mean, I guess,
but it's not likely.
They're about 20 years
older than we are.
[OKABE] In that case,
I would place my bet against it.
[YUKI]
That's right, the song.
I figured it'd be easier
just to call you up and ask.
Oh, sure one sec,
I'll put him on.
Here.
[YUKI giggles]
[WOMAN]
Yes? Hello?
[OKABE]
U-Um. Sorry to bother you.
My name's Okabe,
and I'm a friend of Amane's.
--[WOMAN] Okabe?
--Right.
I know this is odd,
but I wanted to ask you
about that, uh, song.
[WOMAN]
I know that voice.
Is that you, Rintaro?
Do I sound familiar?
It's me, love!
There's no way! It can't be!
[WOMAN]
Excuse me?
Don't you dare tell me
you didn't recognize
your own mother's
melodious tone!
What a coincidence!
That lady was
your mother all along?
Weird!
In class, everyone just goes
by their first name.
So, tell us about the song.
What did your mother
have to say about it?
Well, it's odd.
[AKEMI]
I learned it from you!
--[OKABE] What?
--[AKEMI] I'm telling you,
you're the one
who sang it to me!
[OKABE]
But that makes no sense!
I don't even know it.
How could I have sung it to you?
[AKEMI]
You don't remember?
It was back when
you were in middle school,
and Mayuri was going
through such a hard time.
She was down in the dumps.
Come to think of it,
you adopted that bizarre
persona around then, too.
What was that
goofy phrase again?
[dramatically]
I am an evil mad scientist!
[OKABE]
Please stop....
[AKEMI] Anyway, you used
to sing that song in the bath.
I could hear you
from the living room!
--[OKABE] Did I really?
--[AKEMI] That's right!
So, it's your fault that
always get it stuck in my head!
But, then,
what exactly does
all of this mean for me?
I wish I knew.
I'm bewildered
that I can't recall
ever having sung it
in the first place.
Have you ever heard him
singing it, Mayuri?
No, it's weird,
I don't remember that either.
[OKABE] It seems we're all in
exact same boat as Kagari, then.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to eavesdrop,
but did she say that Mayuri
was down in the dumps?
That was a pretty
rough time for her.
Hey, Okarin.
Do you think we should
pay someone a visit?
[OKABE] I suppose,
but are you okay with that?
[MAYURI]
Hmm. You never know,
maybe just being there
will jog your memory.
What do you say?
[crossroads bell ringing]
[MAYURI]
Grandmother will be so happy
that you came to
visit her again, Okarin!
She loves you!
[KAGARI] Are we really going
to see your grandmother, though?
[MAYURI] Mm-hmm. I can't wait
to introduce you to her, Kagari,
because I know
she's gonna love you,
just like
she loves Okarin!
She'll be so delighted
to meet you!
Thanks, Mayuri.
[KAGARI]
This is a...
[MAYURI]
Well, Okarin?
Do you remember
anything new?
[OKABE]
Not yet.
[MAYURI]
Too bad...
Well, we're here.
Wanna say hello?
[MAYURI]
Mm-hmm.
This'll only
take a minute.
[MAYURI]
It's been a while, Grandma.
Guess what?
I made a new friend,
and she's here today!
Her name is Kagari.
This is a kind of a
ritual for Mayuri, so...
Ah. A ritual?
Losing the memories from
your childhood must be hard.
We're trying to help her.
But I wonder if she'll
ever get them back.
I couldn't stand
to not remember.
Huh?
[MAYURI gasps]
Ah. Looks like
a downpour, Mayuri.
We'd better run for cover!
[OKABE] That rainstorm
came out of nowhere.
[MAYURI laughs]
We're all completely drenched!
Yeah, it's a shame none of us
thought to bring an umbrella.
[classical music
playing on radio]
Hey! We're not far
from my house.
Let's go there and dry--
[music continues playing]
[MAYURI]
Kagari?
[KAGARI]
This song.
Mommy.
--[OKABE] Kagari?
--[KAGARI] This is--
--[MAYURI] What's the matter?
-- [OKABE] What're you--?
--[horn honks]
--Kagari!
[KAGARI panting]
[KAGARI]
I miss you!
[panting continues]
I miss you so much!
Mommy!
It's you!
[pants]
[MAYURI]
Oh, you're awake!
It's you...
[MAYURI sighs]
Thank goodness!
I'm glad you're up.
I was so worried!
Mommy...
[MAYURI]
What, Kagari?
[KAGARI whimpers]
Mommy!
[sobbing]
Wait, what?
[KAGARI] I missed you
so much, Mommy!
[sobbing]
But I'm not anybody's
mommy yet, Kagari.
[KAGARI]
No. Mommy is my mommy!
I love you! You're the
only mother I know!
Mommy Mayuri! [sobs]
[OKABE] Does this mean...
her memories came back?
I really found you.
Finally!
--[KAGARI wails]
--What? I'm not...
It's all right now.
I'm here.
Everything's gonna be okay.
[KAGARI sobs]
Mommy!
[KAGARI] ♪ Searching for
just one little thing. ♪
--♪ The-- ♪
--[BOY] Uh, pardon?
Ah. What's that song?
[sighs] The way you were
singing it was nice.
So pretty.
[KAGARI]
It's Mommy's.
[gasps]
[KAGARI]
I love my mommy,
and it's her song.
[thunder rumbles]
[MAN]
Runaway K6205.
Shiina Kagari.
The girl has been located.