[MAHO]
It's theoretically possible.
However, theory and actuality
are two different things.
To leap to 2011,
the toll on your mental health
alone would be colossal.
Even if we take the
improvements into account
that enable you to leap
two weeks in one go.
In order to go back
a single year,
you would have to make
more than 20 leaps.
That's less than
a tenth of the goal.
Then, once you reach the
period prior to the upgrade,
you'll only be able to leap
48 hours at a time.
Add that up and...
It's gonna take me around
3,000 leaps to reach 2011.
[MAHO]
That's an absurd amount.
[DARU]
You're really going back?
Yeah.
If I intend to change this
world, I have no other choice.
It appears you're resolute.
Well, long time no see,
Okabe Rintaro.
Kurisu?
The entire time
you were in a coma,
she was monitoring your vitals
and making sure
you didn't die on us.
Just so you know.
Amadeus watched me?
[AMADEUS] I can't fight
for the cause physically.
I had to do something.
[OKABE]
But still, for 11 years?
That's a long time.
Time is meaningless to me,
and monitoring patterns
like that is fun,
so it was no sweat.
[MAHO]
Also, she'll be your partner
for the long journey ahead.
A sort of checkpoint,
along the way.
So, rest assured that, no matter
how many times you leap back,
until you reach 2025,
she'll be right there,
ready and able to assist you
every time you wake up.
[AMADEUS]
But be gentle.
When you woke up this time,
you broke my
terminal, you brute.
Each time you come to,
if you'll just let me know
that you got there
via time leaping,
I'll do whatever I can to help.
We'll get you back
to 2011. 'Kay?
[AMADEUS]
What?
[OKABE]
Nothing. It's just...
That reminded me of a similar
conversation I had once before.
[OKABE]
I won't run.
Not any longer.
[OKABE]
Mayuri once said
it wasn't right for me to carry
the full weight of this alone.
Somewhere along the way,
her kindness became
an excuse for me.
But now?
I see that the only reason
I'm still standing
is my friends were there.
I'm alive, and I owe that
to their adamant
refusal to give up.
No one ever forced me
to bear the future alone.
These people are
willing to help me,
and the future
belongs to them, too.
You ready?
Yes. Do it.
[key clicks]
[groans]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[AMADEUS gasps]
Okabe!
When did you wake up?
Easy, no sudden movements.
You've been lying in a coma
for the past 11 years,
so all your muscles
have atrophied.
You shouldn't be up.
[OKABE]
Listen to me.
[AMADEUS gasps]
I'm here from two
weeks in the future
using the time leap machine.
Huh?
Time leap machine?
Damn it! Future me is in for
such a royal ass kicking!
[OKABE]
Let me explain.
I traveled here from two
weeks in the future
using the time leap machine.
I had woken up then, too.
I spoke with Daru and Hiyajo.
I'm aware that it's
now the year 2036,
and I've learned
what the world's become
since I fell into the coma.
And I also know that...
...you have been
watching over me,
monitoring my vitals for
the past 11 years without fail.
[gasps] Uh, I...
I admit that I find
that hard to believe, but--
You must believe me.
Because it's the truth.
You're really from the future?
I need a favor.
[footsteps]
[BOTH gasp]
Okabe. You're--?
Kyouma!
You must've been worried.
I'm sorry.
[RUKA]
You're finally awake!
[FARIS]
Is this real?
[BOTH crying]
--[MAHO gasps]
--Okarin?
So, it is true, you really
came out of it!
Yes. Back from the dead.
Did you happen to get
the message from Amadeus?
[BOTH gasp]
Uh, yeah.
Is what she said right?
You really wanna
go back to 2011?
Yes, and I'm already apprised
of the fact that it'll take me
3,000 leaps to get there.
[BOTH gasp]
And do you know the risks?
It's very dangerous.
[OKABE]
Please help me.
[MAHO]
I just realized.
You'll be explaining
all this 3,000 times
with every leap you make.
[AMADEUS]
Not only that,
but every time he
wakes up in this period,
he'll feel the pain
of coming out of a coma.
You sure about this?
[RUKA]
Okabe.
Rukako.
[RUKA]
Yes?
There's no such thing
as a fixed future.
So don't give up.
A path will open,
I'm certain of it.
[gasps]
Okabe! When on earth
did you wake up? Easy!
You're about to say,
"No sudden movements,"
and that I've been in a coma
for the past 11 years
and my muscles
have all atrophied.
Aren't you?
[gasps]
Does that mean...?
[MAHO] You won't be able
to leap the same way
you have up to this point.
Because two weeks before today,
you weren't anywhere
near the building.
Where was I, then?
[MAHO]
I don't know.
The peacekeeping
squad caught you.
That happened right about
the time you'd be leaping to.
It wasn't until yesterday
that we found you,
already in a coma,
from the torture.
In other words, for the span
of time between my arrest
and when you all rescued me...
[DARU]
You won't be able to leap.
And I don't see how you'd be
able to take a phone call
after you're captured, either.
[MAHO] Until you're rescued,
safely transported here,
and successfully connected
to the monitoring terminal
and Amadeus, there's no way.
[DARU]
Sorry.
If only we'd been
a little bit faster.
Had we gotten you out
of there one day sooner,
we could've sent you on your way
with plenty of time to spare.
I feel terrible.
I'm equally at fault for
failing to further improve
the time leap machine.
I just couldn't do it.
Two weeks is my best.
Three hundred and thirty-six
hours isn't nearly good enough.
I let you down.
Like hell you did.
In fact, you don't know
how grateful I am
that you were able
to manage a two-week leap.
That's more than
Kurisu ever could.
She only figured out how to
go back as far as 48 hours.
So you'd better
be proud of yourself.
Yeah!
[MAHO]
That's not my only concern.
There's still
the possibility that,
if the world-line gets
altered, even slightly,
then the existing situation
could be compromised,
and you could end up
losing your life.
If that happened,
it might change the past.
I understand.
[OKABE]
Regardless, I'm going back.
I've already come
this far from 2036.
I've covered 11 years
in hundreds of leaps.
And with the help of my friends
every step of the way,
I've gotten where I am.
[YUKI]
Okarin!
Huh?
I'm so happy to know
that you're all right!
I appreciate that.
Listen, my friends!
Every one of you have
fought wholeheartedly.
Against all odds.
So please, don't ever give up!
I will show you...
...that the future
can be changed!
[gasps]
[OKABE]
Initiate leap!
Here we go!
[screams]
[gunfire]
[DARU]
Are you there?
[gunfire]
[FARIS]
Kyouma!
We're all heading to
the rendezvous point now!
We'll be waiting for
you there, so hurry!
Be careful.
What? Okabe?
Aren't you in the middle
of the operation?
[OKABE]
Listen closely.
I just leapt here
from the future.
[AMADEUS]
What?
[OKABE] I understand that
might be hard to believe,
but I don't have time
to convince you.
You'll just have to trust me,
because I need your help.
Okay. Wha--?
[OKABE]
In a little while,
I will be captured
by peacekeeping squads,
who will then proceed
to torture me to death.
[gasps]
What should I do?
There has to be something.
Some way to escape that fate
and change the outcome.
[AMADEUS] Well, we do know
why you get caught.
Because we've heard it
from you time and again.
Okabe Rintaro dies,
but not before the year 2025.
You've always used that
fact to your advantage.
You've risked it all and lived.
But if today is the culmination
of these events you've foreseen,
that kernel of information
that's been your protector
all this time will turn
against you, as predicted.
It seems no matter what you do,
the world line will converge.
And you'll still get captured
by the Organization.
Yes, but even so--
[AMADEUS]
I've got it.
Do you think you can
give me ten minutes?
I have a plan.
All Right. Sure.
[AMADEUS]
Good.
And in that time...
[AMADEUS] ...memorize this
map of enemy positions.
Wait. What would
the point of that be?
[AMADEUS]
Are you trying to be obtuse?
Am I not the one who typically
guides you to safety?
If we assume they've set
a trap for you,
there's an high probability
that your death
is a direct result of being
in communication with me.
In which case...
[OKABE] I need to uninstall
the Amadeus app.
[AMADEUS]
Yes, and for good measure,
you'd better remove
your radio battery.
That might be enough
to throw them off.
Another thing.
Use the others as decoys?
But I refuse!
[AMADEUS]
Relax!
So you did just tell me you
came from the year 2036,
time leaping the entire
way, didn't you?
Yeah.
[AMADEUS] So, you've seen
for yourself that your friends
are alive in the future.
Therefore, you know
they can't die today.
Still!
[FARIS]
It's okay, Kyou-meow!
Kurisu already filled us all in.
We're running circles around
the city to confuse the enemy!
So you had better make
a bee-line for the lab
and get to the time-leap
machine right meow!
It's dangerous! You can't just--
[DARU]
Okarin!
This is the part where
you shut your mouth
and put your faith in us!
[OKABE]
Daru.
[SOLDIER 1] The target's
marker just disappeared.
He's not on our GPS.
He must've disconnected
the Amadeus app.
Teams one and two,
head toward his last known
location, immediately!
Our top priority is
capturing the target!
Your orders are to ignore
all other Valkyrie members,
if need be, as long as
we get Okabe Rintaro!
[SOLDIER 3] Target acquired!
Hold on, that can't be!
[ALEXIS]
What's wrong?
Multiple markers for Okabe
Rintaro suddenly appeared!
[SOLDIER 2]
Two? No, three?
Now they're just popping up
all over the place!
[SOLDIER 1]
What does that mean?
[SOLDIER 2]
I-I have no idea!
But Amadeus just came back
out of nowhere!
Rintaro.
[OKABE]
I will never give up again.
Nor will I lie to myself
any longer.
I am done pretending I made
the right choice back then,
and I refuse to
compromise further!
[OKABE] They've all been
battling desperately,
onward through it all.
Driven by a glimmer of hope
that this world can be changed.
I will place my faith
in that hope.
Their courage
will be my strength!
I will show everyone
that our bond
will carry us to Steins Gate!
[DARU]
Okarin.
[SUZUHA]
Uncle Okarin.
[MOEKA]
Okabe.
[FARIS]
Kyouma!
[RUKA]
Okabe.
[KAGARI]
Okarin.
Okarin!
Okabe.
I won't give up!
[OKABE screaming]
--[door bangs]
--[OKABE panting]
[BOTH gasp]
Whoa, buddy.
[MAHO]
Dramatic entrance, much?
[OKABE]
Daru. Hiyajo.
[MAHO]
Hm?
I need to be punched.
What? Like, again?
Uh, I'd rather not repeat--
[OKABE]
Don't you dare hold back!
Put every ounce of your pent-up
anger and resentment into it!
Your worry for Suzuha.
I want you to take all that
and hit me in the face with it!
I'd have pegged
you for a sadist.
You know I deserve it. Right?
I've had my head in the
sand this whole time.
I've been letting fear
run me around,
so I've earned a good clout.
You're crazy, but... okay.
Don't do it!
[MAHO gasps]
Now.
[growls]
Let it fly!
[MAHO gasps]
[DARU]
Uh.
You knocked him out.
[OKABE chuckling]
[BOTH]
Hmm?
[OKABE]
Ah, sweet inertia.
It would appear that
you're my right-hand man
in more ways than one,
dearest hack.
I have just time-leapt back here
from the distant future.
[DARU]
You okay, Okarin?
[OKABE]
Oh, not so, Daru.
[MAHO]
Uh...
[chuckling]
[DARU]
That cackle stirs my soul!
[gasps]
[MAHO]
Huh?
[OKABE laughing]
[OKABE]
You shall call me Kyouma!
[MAHO]
Kyouma?
[OKABE]
Yes.
Otherwise known as
lab member 001!
The demiurge of this devil's
workshop! Anarchy incarnate!
Archon buffeted by
the passions of chaos!
And the consummate
mad scientist himself.
[DARU squeals]
I am the one and only...
Houoin Kyouma!
[MAHO]
Whoa.
What the... fresh hell?
Bitchin'!
Huh?
[OKABE]
You! The Lilliputian!
--Me?
--[OKABE] Yes, you!
[OKABE]
Would anyone else in this room
answer to such a moniker?
Fetch me my lab coat.
Do it at once!
Uh! Hey!
You could ask nicely!
[OKABE]
Behold, my sacred white armor,
bestowed upon me by the fates!
The moment my arms slide
through their hallowed sheaths,
I will truly awaken
from my slumber!
[laughing]
Oh, man!
So, um, care to
explain? What's this?
He's reverted back
to the old Okarin.
The Okarin who's crazy
and nonsensical.
Taken by flights
of delusional fancy.
Our true leader has
returned to us at last!
[OKABE] You complete the time
leap machine, minions.
My presence here serves
as irrefutable proof.
Lilliputian!
[MAHO]
Okay! That's enough!
As of this moment, I officially
bequeath this title to you:
Lab member 009.
You are forthwith a hand
of Hououin Kyouma,
and shall aid
in our operations.
Hiyajo Safina.
[MAHO]
What? Who the hell is that?
And now! I call a
round table meeting!
Summon forth all the other
lab members at once!
[FARIS]
What's going on meow?
[RUKA]
Yeah, um...
Would you mind telling us why
you brought us all here, Okabe?
[OKABE]
It's Kyouma!
[gasps]
[OKABE] Because a new operation
is about to commence!
And for it to succeed,
every lab member must
do their part, understood?
So where are Suzuha and Mayuri?
And Moe-meow texted me
saying she was busy, too.
Shiina had to, uh--
Despair not, friends!
Though these absences
are to be expected,
the operation must
take place as planned,
lest the planet be doomed!
Ah! So the red star
I saw glowing...
[OKABE] I hereby proclaim
this Operation Vega!
[MAHO] You want us to
recover Amadeus' data?
Indeed.
If you must confirm it,
she's left a cryptic
message on @channel.
Leskinen has already
spirited her away.
[MAHO]
Huh? The professor?
But why would he do that?
It's confirmed!
And just like you said, the
occult board has been hacked!
The Organization has
even tipped their hand
by jamming cellular
phone signals
all throughout Akihabara.
And so, Faris!
Meow?
[OKABE]
Deploy the neighborhood watch
to the Radio Building's
perimeter.
They should see several
suspicious-looking foreigners
in the vicinity.
Relay the intelligence
back here.
We must rely on pay phones
for the duration!
Roger that, meow!
Wait, the Radio Building?
Mayuri and the Part-time Warrior
are headed there as we speak.
[DARU, MAHO gasp]
[MAHO]
No! We have to stop them!
Such an attempt
would be in vain.
Convergence will likely bring
about the same end result.
There is but one means by which
to save them now. Yes.
Huh?
[OKABE]
Kyouma here. Right.
The operation has
a sole objective.
To ensure that Mayuri and Suzuha
depart safely from the roof,
into the past.
Yes, I am aware.
Never again.
That mistake cost me too much.
El.
Psy.
Congroo.
[OKABE]
Mr. Braun!
[BRAUN]
Huh? What's wrong with you?
Soon as I start to think you
might be normal, there ya go.
I've no time to engage
in petty chicanery.
This cellular outage is
the Organization's handiwork.
Stratfor. DURPA.
I implore you for assistance,
Mister Ferdinand Braun!
Well?
[DARU]
Just like Okarin said,
the data seems
to have disappeared.
But if I can just find out
where it's been hidden...
I'll leave your tea here
for when you want it.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it. I can't
do much else to help out.
[MAHO]
That's not true at all.
Remember what
Okabe said earlier?
Rukako, I am counting on you
to support the
technical operatives.
[RUKA]
Support?
Indeed. A job for a stout
heart and gentle demeanor.
A vital mission.
I wondered why everyone
was so excited
to have this strange
version of Okabe back,
but now I think I'm
starting to understand.
[DARU]
Hell yeah!
You better believe! Found it!
That's mission complete!
Urushibara! It's time
to get the word out!
I'm on it!
[VOICEMAIL] You have one
missed call and message.
[machine beeps]
[RUKA] Hey, Kyouma.
Hashida just located Amadeus.
We should be able to recover
the data shortly.
He said not to worry.
[OKABE]
Perfect.
With that in place...
Wait for me there, Mayuri.
I vow to save you this time.
Suzuha?
[SUZUHA]
Just don't move.
Luckily the ricochet
only grazed you,
but you're still losing
a lot of blood.
[clapping]
Excellent work!
To think she could take care
of them all on her own.
The brainwashing
techniques in the future
certainly are incredible.
[SUZUHA]
You're the one.
You did this! You hurt Kagari!
That's right. Hashida Suzuha,
soldier of Valkyrie.
Kagari was my little spy
long before you began
your epic journey
with her into the past.
That is, she was a spy
for my future self.
While your anger is justified,
I simply haven't the time
to indulge it.
Sorry.
I'll make it easy on you.
Soon, you'll no longer
be plagued
by the bitterness of the future
or the grief of the past.
Or perhaps,
you'd prefer that I wipe
your mind clean of all this?
That's right, a little tampering
with your synapses,
and it's all gone.
What?
[ALEXIS]
Rintaro.
Uncle Okarin?
Okarin.
[gasps]
[ALEXIS] Yes, I must
echo their surprise.
This is quite odd.
Who tipped you off?
[OKABE] Kagari won't
be joining you today.
[ALEXIS gasps]
[OKABE]
Sorry.
We've restrained her elsewhere.
While you were delivering
your speech,
we were taking measures
to secure the Radio Building.
Mr. Leskinen,
you may have considered
yourself not unlike a god
with unrivaled omniscience,
but allow me to disabuse
you of that notion,
for all your schemes
have been foiled.
Now, Rintaro, what is this?
Do you think you'll
get away with it?
--[electricity crackles]
--[ALEXIS yells]
[MAYURI]
Okarin?
Hear me, lab member 002,
Shiina Mayuri!
[MAYURI gasps]
[OKABE]
Operation Arclight.
[gasps]
[OKABE] I leapt back
through time to find you,
and I know all about it.
[MAYURI]
Do you really?
[OKABE]
In less than 30 minutes,
this whole place
becomes a war zone.
So hurry!
Are you serious?
I'll deal with Kagari
myself somehow!
Take care of Mayuri.
You mean it?
I promise.
[OKABE]
Success.
They should make it out safely.
The time machine will
vanish into the past.
Into history.
[OKABE]
It's finished.
[OKABE gasps]
It can't be! It's too early!
[OKABE]
Mayuri!