[classical music playing]
[MAHO]
Amadeus and Salieri.
Kurisu and me.
[MAHO] One of those composers,
Amadeus Mozart
was blessed
with natural genius.
The other,
Antonio Salieri, was not,
and he viewed Mozart
as his lifelong rival.
That's K331.
Mozart's Piano Sonata
Number 11.
Movement One, A Major.
I didn't realize you were
a fan of his music.
[MAKISE] Yeah, I am.
I love it, actually.
One of my favorite quotes is
"Death means not getting
to listen to Mozart."
I don't think I've ever
heard that one.
Well, there's no hard proof
that Einstein
actually said those words,
but I don't really care.
I think it's a highly
logical statement,
so I like it regardless.
[MAHO]
Logical?
I mean, you can't
listen to Mozart
when you're dead,
you know.
Yeah, but I'd just
call that obvious.
Right?! Blatantly obvious.
If you're dead,
you can't listen.
It's a true statement.
Huh?
[MAKISE]
Makes perfect sense.
[MAHO]
On July 28th, 2010...
...Makise Kurisu was ripped
from this world.
[MAHO]
Amadeus and Salieri.
The story of those two men
holds special meaning for me.
[MAHO]
I loved Kurisu.
Adored her, even.
[MAHO]
But on top of that,
I respected her.
I aspired to be like her.
[MAHO]
And yet, I...
[MAHO] Hmm? "Global Brain
Science Organization
Office Prep Room.
A fundraising plea by
Professor Alexis Leskinen.
If everyone who happens
to read this poster
would donate
a single dollar,
then I will eat a can of Oden."
The Professor never gets tired
of joking around, does he?
[ALEXIS]
Yo, Maho!
I'd like to welcome you to our
new powered-up prep room.
[MAHO] Are you referring
to the coffee table and couch?
Yes! It calls to mind
one of my favorite quotes.
"Keeping it simple is the secret
on the long journey
towards truth."
[MAHO] And whose words
would those be?
They're mine, naturally.
[laughs]
Anywho, how's Amadeus?
I just finished running
the final system checks.
We should be able to
launch it now with no issues.
--You want me to do that?
--Of course!
[whirring, beeps]
[keyboard clacking]
[chimes]
Long time, no see.
Hi, ma'am!
Well, no complications yet?
[AMADEUS]
Negative.
Or none that
I'm aware of in any case.
All good here.
Good indeed.
I'll let Okabe know
everything's in order now.
[AMADEUS] Great, but even
if he knows that I'm restored,
I'm still not certain that
he'll be willing to talk.
Why say that?
I get the feeling
he likes talking to you
a whole lot more than me.
And the feeling seems mutual.
[MAHO] Hmm? Can you please
stop saying stuff like that?
As I've told you before,
it's fallacious.
[AMADEUS] But based on
my observation and analysis,
I believe it's a highly
probable deduction.
[MAHO]
I beg to differ!
You're just getting swept away
by your own delusional
love fantasies.
[laughs]
I sure have missed hearing
you two go head-to-head.
Right! Time to get
this meeting underway.
--[MAHO] Yes.
--[AMADEUS] Sure.
[OKABE]
The hell is this?
[MAYURI gasps]
U-Uh...
This room is a disaster!
[MAHO]
Oh, hi, Okabe!
Aren't you a little early?
[phone beeps]
[sighs]
[OKABE] You've made
this place a dump.
I think it's even worse
than it was a few days ago.
[MAHO] Nothing goes unchanged
by the passage of time.
What do you think?
Puts the "fun"
in functional, right?
[MAYURI]
I could get lost in this mess!
[MAHO] Anyway,
Amadeus is fully restored now.
-Is that so?
-What do you say?
If you wanna
continue testing it,
then I can reinstall
the app for you.
[inaudible]
Yes, please do.
You don't have to, you know.
It's quite all right.
A lot's happened since then.
I've been thinking
it's about time
that I got on with my life.
So, why do you think
Faris insisted
I bring Mayuri
with me today?
[giggles]
Because I always know
just how to get things done!
I think I see
what her plan was.
She had one goal in mind:
to get this room cleaned up!
And if you're here
that's bound to happen?
I think it's more that
if I came here to help,
I would most likely
bring a certain
special someone
along with me!
Who would that be?
Sergeant Clean!
The "Get It Clean" Queen!
[military drums playing]
Sergeant Clean's
in charge now, maggots!
It's time to whip
this place into order!
Oh, Nae, is that you?
[NAE]
Listen up!
Until this room sparkles,
I don't wanna hear
you say anything
except "Yes, ma'am!"
As far as I'm concerned,
all you're good for is
squirming around in garbage.
You're the lowest of the low,
and you answer to me!
You got that, punk?!
What is going on?
That's Sergeant Clean.
Nae's been known to become
a whole different person
when she does housework.
That's an understatement.
[DARU]
But if we do a good enough job,
maybe she'll reward with us
with a little more than
just her usual sweetness.
Who invited you here, hack?
No talking!
Did somebody say
something creepy?
[DARU whimpers]
Me! It was me, Sergeant!
Wipe that stupid
smirk off your face!
I've got an idea!
From now on, I'm gonna
call you "Mr. Smiley Bear."
You like that,
Mr. Smiley Bear?
Yes, I do, Sergeant Clean!
That's just dandy,
Mr. Smiley Bear!
Now get your butt
into the hall
and sweep the whole thing
up and down ten times!
Sir, yes, sir!
Right away, Sergeant Clean!
He's enjoying this way more
than is appropriate.
[MAHO] What, exactly,
is the point here?
Almost forgot.
You and Kiryu are supposed
to vacate the premises
till we're done.
Huh?
No one told me that.
Orders are from the home owner.
So you can't refuse.
[NAE] You call that clean,
Mr. Smiley Bear?
[MAHO]
So, what's up?
You uncover anything else?
[OKABE]
No new developments.
I've got a hunch
as to the culprits,
but without solid evidence,
I can't be sure.
Wouldn't want another
SERN situation.
[MAHO]
SERN?
[OKABE]
Oh, uh, nothing. Never mind.
[MAHO]
Okay.
I still can't seem to wrap
my head around everything.
I never would have thought
Kurisu would be
researching time machines.
[OKABE]
It's the truth.
[MAHO]
I didn't accuse you of lying.
It just seems so crazy,
that's all.
Though I should just
expect it by now.
[keyboard clicking]
[OKABE]
Salieri?
[MAHO] It's my username
for the college's online portal.
I thought I told you that.
Oh, right.
Does it have
special significance?
Not really.
Okay.
[MAHO]
Antonio Salieri.
The man known primarily
for his obsession
with Amadeus Mozart.
Heard of him?
[OKABE] Yeah, isn't there
a movie about that?
From the '80s?
[MAHO]
That's the one.
Salieri showed promise,
in his own right,
as a court composer in Vienna.
But his envy
of Mozart's talent
drove him to despair.
In the end, Salieri's
hounding and interference
are said to have brought
about Mozart's demise.
[OKABE]
Are you saying...?
[MAHO sighs]
Don't worry.
It's not as dark
as you might be thinking.
But still...
[OKABE grunts]
[gasps]
Okabe?
Hi!
[OKABE]
Hi. It's been a minute.
You haven't changed at all.
Yeah. Same to you.
[AMADEUS]
Duh, of course, I haven't!
--I'm AI, remember?
--[computer chimes]
[MAHO]
I don't know.
It doesn't feel right at all.
I'm just gonna
have to rearrange it
to my liking later.
The others would kill you
if they heard you
disrespecting their work.
Okarin! Sorry we kept you.
[OKABE] The Taskmaster
pooped out, huh?
Yep!
I guess the Sergeant Clean act
really takes
it out of this one.
[DARU] Want me to
carry her now?
Sure, if you want a full-force
haymaker to the head
from Mr. Tennoji,
then be my guest.
The full-force haymaker
to the head?
[DARU breathes heavily]
All those
cleaning products must have
scrambled his brains,
the poor sod.
[MAYURI] If you can't find
something you need,
let me know and I'll tell you
where we put it.
Thanks for that.
Where did Faris and Kiryu go?
[MAYURI] Dunno, but they said
they'd be right back.
--[FARIS] Meow!
--[OKABE] Hmm?
--Kyouma! [giggles]
--[OKABE grunts]
Haven't I told you
not to call me that?
[MOEKA]
We've returned.
[OKABE] I noticed.
What's with the bags?
Faris said she wanted
to go shopping,
--so...
--[FARIS giggles]
Sorry, but no boys
are allowed
at our slumber party.
Not even Kyouma, meow.
Your slumber party?
Yep! Meow!
That's our code
for top secret operation.
Meow!
The all-girl all-night
Cinderella secret party!
Someone's gonna get sleepy
and spill her guts.
Meow!
[BOTH groaning]
What the heck's
your problem, ladies?
Why aren't you all excited?
Come on! I even picked out some
super fancypants ice cream
and pastries for us!
[MAHO]
If you insist.
Maho-meow's luckier
than the rest of us.
She's tiny like
a cute little doll,
so everything
looks good on her.
I told you!
Quite calling me that!
[MOEKA chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
Did she smile?
Moe-meow finally
showed emotion!
--[giggles]
--No. Please stop it.
Wow! Check out those tatas.
Your boobs are magnificent
and they're just
begging to be tickled.
--[giggles]
--Stop! Please.
No. Don't!
Uh-oh. This is making me feel
kinda naughty, meow! I think
--the feeling is mutual, too.
--Hey, stop. Quit, please!
[giggling]
I'm gonna go get some juice.
[panting]
That was bizarre.
Putting it in your diary?
A memo for my novel.
A novel?
You're a writer?
Mm, I'm not special.
I could be easily replaced.
If I invent a fictional life,
it might give mine meaning.
What are you talking about?!
Your life has meaning!
And nobody could
ever replace you!
But I--
You're unique and important,
so knock it off!
If you always compare
yourself to others,
you'll waste your life
feeling inferior!
And you're not! [gasps]
[sighs]
Just... never mind.
[FARIS snoring]
[sleepily]
No. Please.
[FARIS sleepily]
I think she likes it, meow.
[OKABE]
It's quite alright.
A lot's happened since then.
[OKABE]
I've been thinking...
...it's about time that
I got on with my life.
Why is he like that?
[gasps]
[MAHO]
This circuit board!
Look what a beautiful
pattern it makes!
Like a work of art!
Holy crap! Is this an
IFX 008 image sensor?
What on Earth
is it doing here?!
[OKABE]
Uh, yeah, crazy.
[MAHO] Who knew Akihabara
had cool places like this?!
[AMADEUS]
Now you've seen it.
Miss Maho in all her glory.
[OKABE]
Who knew she was obsessed
with random
computer circuitry?
I love building
with electronics.
When I was a kid,
I spent most of my time
putting together
those little kits, you know?
[AMADEUS] Oh,
ever build a germanium radio?
Yeah, I burned myself pretty bad
soldering a few of those.
[AMADEUS giggles]
Happens to the best of us!
Damn right! [laughs]
[OKABE] You two might be
the only ones.
[MAHO sighs]
[MAHO]
I'm kicking myself
for not coming
out here before now.
Although I should kick you
for not telling me.
[OKABE]
Well, how was I to know
you were
electronically inclined?
[MAHO]
Are there any more shops
that sell computer parts?
[OKABE]
Once upon a time,
there were little parts stores
all over the place,
but lately, it seems...
Never mind.
Didn't you want to talk
to me about something?
It can wait.
You don't have
anywhere to be, right?
Let's hang out for a bit longer.
Well, I have no objections
to that, but...
[giggles]
[gasps]
Hey! Check it out!
[OKABE]
An at-channel character?
[MAHO]
Is that what it's called?
I just remembered!
Kurisu had one of these
little guys in her bedroom!
[OKABE]
Kurisu did?
She must've had one
sent to America, then.
[gasps]
Miss Maho! Say no more!
Spoken just like a
true closet at-channeler.
Huh? What are you
even talking about?
What's an at-channeler?
--♪ Never gonna-- ♪
--♪ Give-- ♪
[gasps]
Okabe!
You know
you deserved it.
Do you mind if I give
this claw thingy a try?
Now then.
I've just gotta
pick it up with the claw
and drop it over the opening,
and that's that, right? 'Kay!
[machine whirring]
[MAHO groans]
What the--?
How is this
contraption breaking
the basic laws of physics?
[OKABE laughs] That is how
they turn a profit, you know.
[MAHO] All right. I think
I loosened it up last time.
Next turn, that thing's
mine, for sure!
--Huh?
--Gotta get some more change!
We've lost her
to the claw monster, it seems.
[AMADEUS]
This is no time to waste
on dumb jokes, act fast!
Now's the perfect chance
to prove that you're man enough.
C'mon, get it!
Wait. Why me?
Awesome, this should be
just enough to--
Someone came
and knocked it loose.
I was able to get it out
on the first try.
Here ya go.
Are you sure?
Trust me, I have no desire
to keep this thing.
Okay, if you insist.
[MAHO giggles]
Did you really
want it that badly?
Yeah, but it's
not actually for me.
After Kurisu died,
her mom put one
in her bedroom.
She knew how much
Kurisu loved these,
and it made her feel better.
But it was lost in the fire.
I didn't know
there was a fire.
That's why...
...I wanted to give it to
Kurisu's mom as a present.
Is that all right?
Of course.
What a nice thought.
[gasps]
Uh, wanna go inside?
They have a couple
sweet racing games.
[MAHO] I totally
lost track of time in there.
[OKABE] Man, do you have a
secret life as a pro drag racer?
You beat every high score.
[MAHO]
I just like racing games,
but I can get carried away.
[OKABE]
What should we do next?
You wanna grab
a bite or something?
No.
It's already way later
than I had planned to stay out.
But there's something
I need to do
before I go back home.
I can't leave for America
until I do.
[OKABE]
This place?
[MAHO]
Yeah.
The building where
Makise Kurisu lost her life.
Where she drew
her last breath.
If you'd rather not go in,
that's fine.
I'll go alone,
just say where.
[OKABE]
No.
[MAHO] It's quieter
than I expected.
[OKABE] Most of
the shops already moved
'cause it's getting
torn down soon.
No one really
uses it these days.
[OKABE whimpers]
[OKABE]
Follow me.
This is where it happened.
So, she died here?
[sighs]
Kurisu...
[MAHO] I'm not
a physicist or anything,
so I don't fully understand
all the ins and outs
of the theory
of general relativity.
But, if space
and time are unified,
why can't we travel
though time the same way
we're able to move around
so freely in space?
Right now,
I'm standing on
the same spatial axis
where Kurisu died.
And yet, just because the
temporal axis is slightly off,
I can't stop her death
from happening.
[OKABE] It would
make no difference.
If you were on the same
axis of time and space,
you'd still be powerless.
How can you be
so sure about that?
[OKABE] I discussed it
with Kurisu.
Oh.
[OKABE sobbing]
Kurisu.
[gags]
Okabe! Are you all right?
[gasps]
[OKABE sobbing]
[MAHO]
Wh-What can I do?
[OKABE muffled]
Forgive me.
[MAHO]
There's nothing to forgive.
I can see how much
you cared for Kurisu.
This is all my fault.
I'm the one
who brought us here.
[OKABE]
No, don't worry about it.
Hey.
Did you really just
meet Kurisu at a seminar?
[OKABE inhales deeply]
Cause it doesn't
seem that way,
and I wonder...
how long did you and Kurisu
actually know each other?
For a month? Two, maybe?
No, the way you talk about her
leads me to believe
it was a lot longer
than that.
Maho, I--
[MAHO] How do you know
so much about her?
--I can't say.
--[MAHO] Hmm.
Because I'm--
I'm the one who--
[whimpers]
I'm sorry.
I understand.
It's clear something
went on between you two
that you can't talk about.
We can leave it at that.
Thank you, Hiyajo.
[MAHO]
Every time I see you,
I think the same thing.
"Why does Okabe
always look so sad?"
It's worse when
you talk about Kurisu.
But it's there,
no matter who you're with.
As if you're haunted
by some deep regret.
Like you're wrestling
with the past and can't let go.
And the way you are
with me and Mayuri,
it's like you're trying
to protect us
from something we can't see,
or so I thought until
we were really attacked.
You're actually picking up
on all of that?
Yeah.
I'm not naive enough to think
you'd tell me the whole story.
But still,
no matter what
you're going through
I want to help
where I can.
--So that's why--
--Why what?
I promised myself
I would never tell anyone this,
but I will.
I have her--
I have everything that she--
Kurisu's--
Makise Kurisu's legacy.
Her legacy? Hold on.
[MAHO]
Meaning...
...I have Kurisu's laptop.
[MAHO] With all her notes
and theories intact.
Her research data
and her private data, too.
Her personal computer.
[MAHO] The burglar who
broke into my hotel,
that must have been
what they wanted.
[OKABE whimpering]
Where is it?
I can't figure out
her password.
So, I'm having
a trustworthy source
analyze it to try
and hack in.
--No, you can't!
--Huh?
Kurisu's computer
must not be opened!
It's Pandora's Box!
The data inside is a curse
that leads to the annihilation
of the entire globe!
What are you saying?
Don't you hear me?
The race to build
a time machine
leads America and Russia into
deadly conflict with each other!
Both countries are after
the data on that laptop,
and they will stop at nothing
to get their hands on it!
It's the spark
that ignites war.
That brings about
World War III!
I can't believe it.
World War III?