[MAHO] You're saying no
matter how much you leap,
or what you do, the time
machine still gets destroyed?
--[OKABE] Yeah.
--Can't you just get to
the radio building
before Mayushii hops in
and convince her not to
leave in the first place?
[OKABE]
I could, but even though
taking that route might save
both Mayuri and Suzuha...
...I also suspect
it would further
destabilize the situation.
What do you mean?
[OKABE] The destruction
of the time machine
could be a point of convergence.
Perhaps not.
Though, there's no mistaking
that it is a principal event
in the sequence that
sparks World War III.
So, it's highly likely.
[gasps]
Where are you going?
[OKABE]
To get some fresh air.
Clear my head.
Okarin?
You had to leap from
the future over and over
to get back to this
time, didn't you?
Yeah.
In that case, tell me
about the future you!
What are you like in those days?
Delusional and maniacal,
with a laugh like
a pulp supervillain?
Delusional?
I always hoped the old Okarin
would come back someday.
I decided.
Made up my mind
never to give up.
But then, when it really
comes down to it, I--
[AMADEUS]
Oh, get a grip, will ya?
You're so dramatic.
[OKABE]
Kurisu?
Oh, that's right,
I forgot that the professor
hasn't taken her at this point.
[MAHO] You've seen the
future firsthand, right?
Didn't you come back here
specifically to change
its outcomes for the better?
If you call yourself
a scientist,
and there's even the
remote chance of success,
then surrender is not an option.
Just know you have
my full support.
[OKABE chuckles]
[AMADEUS]
What's so funny?
[OKABE]
Nothing.
It's just, no matter what
period I find myself in,
when it comes to you
lab members,
the more the world changes,
the more you all stay the same.
[chuckles]
Huh?
[cackling]
[OKABE]
Imbecile!
Don't you realize
this was merely a wily ruse
to throw the Organization
off my trail?
My faithful assistants!
The first and the second!
Excuse me?
I must call a
roundtable meeting.
Make like shadows and follow!
What's going on? Jeez.
[MAHO]
Yeah.
[OKABE] With alacrity,
my data-driven darlings!
[MAHO grunts]
[OKABE]
To sum up,
these are the two
most consequential factors
that incite World War III.
America and Russia.
Then add in...
the time machine.
You already said that earlier.
[OKABE]
The offending organizations
in this debacle are...
...Stratfor, with Leskinen,
and DURPA, a second
American faction.
Then, there's Russian
Intelligence to consider,
so that makes three
key players in all.
It all seems kinda far-fetched.
Too much like the Organization
you used to rant about.
Precisely.
Perhaps you've forgotten,
but I happen to be a prodigy.
Long have I known
which nations will act
to plunge our realm
into utter pandemonium,
and now, those entities
have begun to move in earnest.
[laughing]
Uh, ma'am?
Yeah, what?
[AMADEUS] Did Okabe sustain
a head injury or something?
Maybe some other form of
trauma, like a fever, or--?
Silence, Miss Christina!
That's not my name!
Aren't you the least embarrassed
to be acting this way?
[OKABE]
You have no idea how much.
Who could behave like such
a moron and not be embarrassed?
[DARU]
I couldn't be happier.
The Okarin I know and love
is the most obnoxious,
annoying tool I've
ever met. It's unreal.
He argues about
literally everything,
and he's delusional
to the bone.
It's ridiculous.
But that might be why
his absurd logic works.
The audacity of it can even
overcome the impossible.
Daru.
[DARU]
Now, explain.
Why did you go out acting like
a sulky pre-teen then come back
with Maho, refreshed,
like your jolly old self again?
What happened out there, buddy?
Friends tell friends
about their exploits!
Didja kiss? You made out, right?
You've got Mayushii,
but you still played
tonsil hockey with Maho!
Nothing even remotely
salacious occurred!
Furthermore, Daru,
aren't you overlooking
a crucial detail here?
[DARU]
Huh?
The name is not
Okabe Rintaro, my friend.
You will call me--whoosh!--
Hououin Kyouma!
--[AMADEUS] Uhh...
--[OKABE] Behold!
[OKABE] May your souls
quaver in the presence
of a true mad scientist!
Peel your orbs and
allow my brilliance
to blister your brains!
Did he finally snap?
[OKABE]
It is I.
The culmination of all
my scheming approaches.
Once set into motion,
it can not be halted,
not even by
the keenest intelligence
of the utmost world powers.
[OKABE chuckles] Yes, indeed.
Who is he talking to?
Enough already.
Spare us the theatrics
and get on with it.
You could've just told me
you didn't want a show.
Princess of Lilliput!
As I was saying before,
the organizations who seek
the time machine
are listed on the board.
All the failures to date
have been caused
in one way or another
by the interference
of said organizations.
But fear not, these entities
can be dealt with--
their impact mitigated.
In terms of the time machine?
Are you saying its destruction
might not be a point
of convergence?
[OKABE]
Here's my idea.
We will allow them both
to board the vessel,
but at the exact moment
the machine initiates
departure to the past,
we must step in and protect
them from interference.
Thus far, we've foiled
Stratfor and Leskinen.
Likewise, we've succeeded in
halting DURPA and its soldiers,
which gives me
a modicum of confidence.
So now there's one left.
We've got to outsmart
the Russians?
Please tell me you've got some
mind-bending plan for that.
[OKABE]
Nope.
[DARU]
For real?
So, you've just been
running your mouth
about your schemes
with no actual scheme?
[AMADEUS] What kind of
mad scientist are you?
[MAHO]
Yeah, deliver.
[OKABE]
Silence, you!
I stopped Leskinen and DURPA!
That speaks to my masterful wit!
My plans congeal over time,
do not rush them!
What've you contributed?
Am I on my own?
Have you three not
a scheme among you?
We didn't have all the
information until just now.
[MAHO sighs]
So, it's come down to this.
[MAHO]
In times like these,
you have to examine
why certain events occur.
Find out what the adversary
means to do,
and then establish
a clear chain of causality.
In this instance,
we've got Russia.
[gasps]
[MAHO] Uh, what they
want is-- It's clear...
Hot damn!
I've been waitin' to see Maho
in this sexy teacher
pose for ages!
[MAHO]
Don't be gross!
Allow me to assist. Here.
[gasps]
Now. Proceed.
--[thudding]
--[OKABE grunting]
[MAHO]
First question.
How did the Russian
and American organizations
find out we're in possession
of a working time machine?
As far as America goes,
they know because of Leskinen.
The Leskinen of the
future used Kagari
to disclose the time
machine's existence
to his present-day counterpart.
That's true, but Kagari would've
made contact with the professor
several years ago at this point.
So why didn't he make
his move back then?
[OKABE] Because nothing
could've been changed.
It would be a time paradox.
If his actions
had defied history,
world line convergence
would swoop in and correct
anything he did
to alter the course.
Convergence.
However, Leskinen's
strategy was to use
that process to his advantage.
Oh, I get it.
What you're saying is,
on July 7th, 2011,
the conflict surrounding
the time machine
comes to a boiling point,
and all parties involved
converge in one place.
And since the time machine
gets destroyed on that same day,
Leskinen thought he could
show up at the right time
and snatch the machine
at the last second.
[gasps]
Do you have any idea where DURPA
could've gotten
their intel, though?
The same way that Stratfor did.
I'm more concerned with
how Russia got theirs.
Could they have just stolen
it from the Americans?
Well, if you consider
the professor found out
about World War III
from his future self
we must assume that the
intel's highly classified.
The last thing
America would want
is for Russia
to get ahold of it.
Daru. Lend your
investigative prowess?
[DARU]
All yours. What're we sleuthing?
We have to locate him.
Doctor Nakabachi.
Fate was certainly
smiling on me.
If this guy hadn't set off
the onboard metal detectors...
I knew it. Doctor Nakabachi
did defect. To Russia.
My dad.
Wait, what?
Let's save that talk for later.
So, Doctor Nakabachi took the
time machine theory, after all,
and turned coat to Russia
in possession of it.
But the catch is,
Russia hadn't developed
anything from it yet.
What do you mean?
[OKABE]
Because if they had succeeded,
there wouldn't be any conflict.
Six months ago,
when we were all attacked.
The Russians destroyed
Kurisu's PC, remember?
They had made a connection
between Nakabachi and Kurisu's
time travel theory.
And they didn't want any other
faction to get ahold of it.
Is there anything of hers
still out there?
Something we may
have overlooked?
Notes she might have taken
in the lab, for example,
or any knowledge she--
[gasps]
Well, it's pretty
clear. Amadeus.
That's what I am, right?
All of Kurisu's
knowledge and memories.
I'm her mind,
thought patterns and all.
If someone wanted
to create a time machine,
they'd want to pick
my brain, for sure.
[OKABE]
That's right.
When Amadeus got taken over,
the world line changed.
[DARU]
What's up?
If we could go back
before Russia got involved,
is there any way we could
protect Amadeus
from being hacked?
[MAHO] Before Russia
got involved? Like, when?
I can't say for certain.
As early as we possibly can.
When did you first start
gathering Kurisu's memory data?
It was before Kurisu
left to come to Japan, so...
That would be around spring
of last year, I think.
[OKABE] If I time-leapt
back to that period...
[DARU]
Can you, though?
We couldn't do that last spring.
[MAHO]
That's right.
The Phone Wave wasn't even
complete until last summer.
Not to mention
the time leap machine.
There's just no way.
You can't go back. Not that far.
I'll send a d-mail then! Daru!
[DARU]
You sure you wanna do that?
You've been so against it
this whole time.
Yes, good point.
SERN will catch on
if we take that route.
And that leads to...
[OKABE grunts]
[MAHO]
Don't worry.
We'll figure out some
other plan of attack.
[DARU]
Uh, so...
I apologize for keeping
this from you until now,
but it might be helpful.
D-RINE?
That's right.
I used the same
principles as D-mail,
but tweaked them to work with
the RINE operating system.
Wait, does that mean
we can send messages
without alerting SERN?
[DARU]
Mm-hmm.
The thing is, RINE was
still just a prototype
in beta last spring.
So, I was the only one in our
group who had the app installed.
Last New Year's might be as
far back as we can send it.
So then, we can't send a message
to anyone but you, can we?
Do you think that'd work?
Possibly.
You'll get a message
from yourself
telling you to hack
into Viktor Chondria.
and to safeguard Kurisu's
data on the servers.
And then, knowing you,
you'll be happy to comply.
I can't let you see it, though,
or you'll lose your shit. Right?
[AMADEUS]
Hold on.
That isn't going to be enough
to stop the info
from getting leaked.
You're up against
a major world power.
As long as there's access,
they'll keep coming after it.
It's also highly likely
they'll replicate it
and distribute it, too.
Yeah, you make a good point.
[MAHO]
What're our other options?
[AMADEUS]
You have to wipe it out.
Hack into the servers and
access Kurisu's memory data
right after the
original back up.
Then cause the system
to self-destruct
so it can never be recovered.
Kurisu?
That's the only way,
ma'am. We have to.
If it's completely wiped out
by spring of last year,
there will be no way
to rebuild Amadeus.
[MAHO] But it would mean
you'll never be...
[OKABE]
Never be, period.
It would effectively stop
Amadeus from ever being built.
[AMADEUS]
What's going on now?
You're asking the wrong person.
You know, if something
doesn't happen soon,
the time machine is going to
be destroyed again tomorrow.
Yeah, that's seeming more
and more likely this go round.
Well then, isn't it obvious
what has to be done?
It is. But still... I understand
where he's coming from.
I mean, I'm sure you do,
too, it's pretty clear.
[MAHO]
I guess.
Poor Okabe.
[phone vibrating]
What's up?
[MAHO] I'm just passing
a message along.
Amadeus wanted me to tell you
that she needs to talk to you.
[phone vibrates]
[gasps]
Hey, Okabe.
[OKABE]
Hey.
You know... it feels like ages
since I've seen the outside.
Do you think you could
show me the view?
There's not much of a
view to speak of, but...
[AMADEUS]
Wow.
What a beautiful place.
[OKABE]
First time out at night?
[AMADEUS]
You really have to ask?
It's not like I have legs.
If I did, I could walk
around all I want.
But I'm only a program.
[AMADEUS] The fact that you're
grappling with the prospect
of erasing me speaks volumes to
Amadeus' efficacy as a system.
To have that kind of influence
on someone's heart?
A person? It seems like my AI
must be almost passably human.
You'll just disappear.
[AMADEUS] I knew you'd be
hung up on that part.
Since we're already outside,
would it be too much
to ask for you
to show me the sights
for a little longer?
[AMADEUS] Everything's so
different than in the daytime.
[OKABE]
Of course it is.
[AMADEUS] Are other parts
of the city like this at night?
[OKABE] Well, it depends
on the prefecture.
Shinjuku and Shibuya
are as bustling at night
as during the day,
but it's usually even quieter
in Ginza than it is around here.
[AMADEUS]
Really? How fascinating.
[OKABE]
Which way, boss?
[AMADEUS]
Let's see. Oh!
Take me up those
stairs over there!
[OKABE]
As you wish.
[AMADEUS] Remember when
you walked me around
like this before,
not long after we met?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
[AMADEUS]
Hey, by the way,
what happened to your funny
mad scientist voice?
All that, "Mwahaha" stuff
and whatnot.
Oh, you like it when
I talk that way?
Assistant?
[AMADEUS]
Please don't.
Unless you like to be
mocked mercilessly.
[OKABE chuckles]
[AMADEUS]
Akiba is an interesting place.
[OKABE]
Are you fond of it?
[AMADEUS]
Rather.
I like the chaotic nature of it,
the lack of rigorous structure.
So opposite to
the place I occupy,
where everything has a specific,
assigned function.
And if something doesn't,
it gets promptly erased.
All the fat gets trimmed
to ensure supreme efficiency
within every process.
The world you've
shown me tonight
is the complete opposite,
a perfect foil to my domain.
Uselessness doesn't
mean extermination.
Utterly wasteful
actions happen daily
from everything I've observed.
One can be fully aware
of the right course of action
and still choose differently.
The ensuing chaos
diversifies outcomes,
lends meaning to what
seemed irrelevant before.
All processes get
jumbled together,
which creates fertile
ground for the miraculous.
Encounters have higher stakes.
A program like myself
could never come close
to replicating those conditions.
[OKABE]
Kurisu.
Listen, Okabe Rintaro.
I can understand
if you feel sentimental,
and it makes perfect sense that
you wouldn't want to erase me.
I won't lie. I feel
kinda happy about that.
Then, maybe--
[AMADEUS]
Quiet.
You've spoken with such fervor
about the Steins
Gate world line.
And Mayuri's life.
Not to mention the original me,
and the life that
was taken from her.
A world line where all
that can be saved
is right in front of you,
begging you to act.
I've said this ad nauseum,
but, it's true:
I am just a program, you know?
Even if you have feel--
[OKABE]
I get it, okay?
Then, why?
[OKABE crying]
Because I-- Back then...
I'm the one who killed
the original you.
[gasps]
[OKABE] In that situation,
I had to choose.
I could only save
Kurisu or Mayuri.
I chose Mayuri in the end,
so... I gave up trying
to save your life.
[AMADEUS] And when you
told me, I agreed with it?
[OKABE] Yeah. You
reassured me repeatedly.
You said I'd made
the right decision.
That choosing Mayuri
wasn't wrong.
In fact, it's what
you wanted me to do.
Sounds about right.
I'm far too proud to let anyone
make sacrifices
for my sake alone.
You know what you have
to do now, don't you?
You've got to save
Mayuri and Suzuha.
You can't allow a world
war to start just--
[OKABE]
But then I'll lose you!
Again!
It'll be like you
never even existed.
[OKABE]
You won't simply be gone...
They'll forget you!
None of them will remember
you were part of their lives.
No. You're wrong.
Because you won't
forget me, will you?
[OKABE]
What happens if I fail?
What if I can't find the
path to Steins Gate?
[AMADEUS]
Isn't that the assumption
you operated under
until recently?
You had given up.
But you regretted it.
And don't forget
that you put yourself
through 3,000 time leaps
to come back and fix it!
Since the original
me was killed,
I find myself in a quandary.
What is the true nature
of my existence, y'know?
What is my purpose in
this strange incarnation?
I can't say it brings me
much joy to know
that I'm the spark that
starts World War III.
It's a total downer,
to be perfectly frank.
I don't want that to be
my only reason for being.
But if it's within my power to
help save the original Kurisu,
and to somehow preserve
this miraculous world...
If that's the answer to
the puzzle of my being,
I'd be happy.
It's logically sound
and even romantic, in a way.
[OKABE]
Kurisu.
Show me the sky.
[AMADEUS gasps]
I can't believe
how brilliant it is!
Yeah.
You all take it for granted,
living in a world
full of breathtaking beauty
that you just overlook.
Time flows on, mingling
with chaos and chance
to create miracles,
and shape fate.
It's almost overwhelming.
[AMADEUS]
Right?
[DARU]
I'm done setting everything up.
Well? Ready?
You sure?
[AMADEUS]
Yes.
[DARU]
Okay.
All that's left to do is
send Maho's attachment
to my past self.
Then that will be that,
if all goes according to plan.
[MAHO]
Amadeus.
Ready input to receive
control code.
Der alte .
Wurfelt nicht .
[alarm blaring]
[AMADEUS] Control code has
been received successfully.
System is now transitioning
into emergency mode.
Run command from Hiyajo Maho,
top level system administrator.
Transfer selected patch program
to designated file.
No, modify command.
Amend to commence
processing upon system reset.
[AMADEUS]
Thank you, ma'am.
Command confirmed.
Executing command from Hiyajo
Maho, top-level administrator.
Initiating protocol
for system reset.
Wait!
The possibilities are endless.
Do your best--never give up!
I know you better
than anyone else, ma'am.
So I can say
with confidence...
...you'll surpass my research,
by leaps and bounds, I'm sure.
You'll accomplish things
my original self
could only dream of!
And then, someday, we'll create
a world that's worthy of us all.
I know we can do it!
I have no doubt
that we'll get there!
[OKABE]
Amadeus, I swear to you!
Upon that promised day,
when time intersects,
I know without a doubt
that we'll reach that place.
And you and I shall meet again!
[AMADEUS] Ma'am!
Take care of him for me!
Our Hououin Kyouma!
Kurisu!
Go!
[screaming]