[ALEXIS, MAHO]
Without further ado,
we would like to demonstrate
the AI named Amadeus.
[MAHO] This system is founded
on cutting-edge theories
proposed by one of our
researchers, Makise Kurisu.
[CROWD murmuring]
[OKABE gasps]
[MAHO]
My apologies.
It will take a moment for
the program to launch properly.
Please remain patient.
Does this mean it's not working?
I'm not surprised, since
the ideas they're presenting
can't be anything
more than a joke.
How do you think they went about
collecting memory samples?
[MAN 02D] From a scientific
standpoint, this is nonsense!
It's not possible
to digitize memories
and swap them around like files!
Your proposal is insane!
I read the ludicrous paper
that was published in Sciency .
The theories don't
hold up. No surprise.
What can you expect
when the lead author
is a 17-year-old girl?
[CROWD laughs]
With all due respect, I--
[OKABE]
Objection!
Huh?
Sir, you can't take it off the
table if you've never tried it!
Our world is full of technology
that people once thought could
only exist in science fiction!
We have those things today
because of researchers
who dared to dream bigger!
Blind criticism like yours
accomplishes nothing!
Uh--
[clapping]
Wonderfully put.
It is thanks to bold ideas...
[MAHO]
Wonderfully put.
It is thanks to bold ideas
and open minds like yours
that science
continues to progress.
You have the sort
of vision necessary
to become the world's
third Einstein.
However, scientists
must always remain calm
in the face of adversity.
Outbursts like yours
should be saved for
those eureka moments when
our experiments succeed.
Thank you all for waiting.
Please turn your
attention to the screen.
It's time for a much better
interpreter to take over.
[CROWD murmuring]
It's a pleasure to meet you,
ladies and gentlemen.
I am Hiyajo Maho.
Or more specifically,
I'm a copy of her from 78 hours
and 22 minutes in the past.
I am her memories.
[CROWD gasps]
[AMADEUS]
In other words,
I know everything Hiyajo Maho
knew roughly four days ago.
I'm an encapsulation
of her mind.
--[MAN 02E scoffs]
--I notice somebody
in the fifth row is snickering.
Yes. You in the red plaid.
I can probably guess
what you're thinking.
You assume my responses
are pre-programmed--
that what all of you are
watching now is just a video.
I'm right, yes?
Others might be wondering
if the human me
is controlling my
actions in real time.
Although, most of you
are likely thinking this:
"Preserving memories as
electronic data is impossible."
Of course, if that
were true, then...
I wonder. What exactly
does that make me?
--[classical music playing]
--[chattering]
[sighs]
[OKABE]
Amadeus.
You want to know my
credit card number?
This is a scam, isn't it?
What age did I stop
taking baths with my dad?
I should report you
for sexual harassment.
No, I can't tell you what
pajamas I wore one week ago.
I don't remember.
[OKABE]
The AI seemed truly conscious.
And stranger, she had
emotional responses
and forgot trivial information.
It's as if she's...
[ALEXIS]
It's our Einstein.
I must know. What did
you think of Amadeus?
Um, if you'll excuse me. Sorry.
[OKABE sighs]
[MAHO, OKABE] I am just not
cut out for this kind of party.
Uh--
Uh--it's you,
from the reception desk.
And you are...?
I'm Okabe Rintaro.
You're Hiyajo.
Am I saying that right?
It's a strange name, isn't it?
Though it is pretty
common in Okinawa.
[OKABE]
You're here for the party?
Uh--yes, I brought something
else to change into.
Or, at least, I'd
planned on doing that.
Madam, I'm sorry for earlier.
[MAHO]
Uh...
[OKABE] For being so rude
as to interrupt your seminar.
Please, don't worry about it.
Things might've been worse
if you hadn't said something.
I would've had to argue
with him myself.
Also, drop the formalities
and loosen up a little, will ya?
Okay, if you say so.
Well, I thought the
seminar was incredible.
To perfect such an advanced
AI is an amazing feat.
[MAHO] Thank you,
but that's not the case.
I assure you the system
is far from perfect.
You had me fooled.
We have loads of
kinks to work out.
For example,
if we tried to implant extracted
memory data into someone,
there'd be no way for
the brain to process it.
[gasps]
[MAKISE] You see, when people
try to access their memories,
the signal goes from the frontal
lobe to the temporal lobe.
You mean top-down
memory search signals.
[gasps] I'm impressed
you know about those.
Certain elements are needed
for transmitted signals
to be utilized by
the temporal lobe.
[MAHO]
And then, of course,
by sending the
copied pseudopulse
to the frontal lobe...
[OKABE] The memory search
signal will function properly.
Is that right?
Tell me. Did you come
to these ideas yourself?
[gasps] Well,
would that be so odd?
[MAHO]
I've heard this theory before.
One of my colleagues proposed
this exact same idea.
But the thing is...
She never published that
hypothesis anywhere.
You came to the same
conclusions she did
and you're not even
in neuroscience.
Coincidence?
[OKABE sighs]
It's not.
Huh?
Everything I said came from
one of Kurisu's lectures.
[MAHO]
Kurisu? Where? When was this?
A while ago, when she was
here as an exchange student.
We became friends and she shared
some of her ideas with me.
So you knew her pretty well.
[OKABE] I did. Sorry if it seems
I was hiding that from you.
--[MAHO] No.
--[gasps]
It's actually
really great to hear.
I'm happy to know that
she was making friends.
We mostly argued,
if you want the truth.
That's so like her.
She'd never admit defeat,
even when she was wrong.
[OKABE] Yeah. Sometimes
arguing just to argue.
She threatened to rip my frontal
lobe out on multiple occasions.
[MAHO chuckles]
[MAHO]
I believe it.
[OKABE]
I bet.
You should've taught
your young researchers
to be more disciplined.
I freely admit that mistakes
were made. Sincerest apologies.
--[OKABE laughs]
--[MAHO sobs]
--[OKABE gasps]
Sorry about this. I know.
Who starts crying
out of nowhere?
[OKABE] Oh... You two...
must've been close.
We were. Sometimes
it's just... so much.
Your nose, too.
[MAHO]
I'm not a child.
[MAHO blows nose]
[ALEXIS]
There you are, Maho!
Huh?
[ALEXIS] I was wondering
where you were hiding.
Ah! You found our Mr. Einstein.
Glad you could make it
to our little party.
[ALEXIS gasps]
Don't tell me you've already
gotten into a lovers' quarrel.
How do you usually settle
things like this in Japan?
No. This is not that.
[MAHO]
You've got it all wrong.
[ALEXIS]
Huh?
It's my fault for crying.
We were talking about
Kurisu... and...
[ALEXIS gasps]
Hold on.
Are you telling me that you
were personally
acquainted with Kurisu?
Uh, yeah, that's right.
[ALEXIS] So you met
her here. Interesting.
And you're a university student.
I attend Tokyo Denki.
My name's Okabe Rintaro.
[ALEXIS]
And during the seminar,
did you speak out
in defense of our work
because it was
based on her ideas?
Oh, no. Not at all.
Actually... I suppose that
might have been part of it.
If that's the case,
then... Maho?
Perhaps it would be a good idea
to introduce Mr. Okabe
to our friend.
To test her.
[gasps]
To test who?
But, Professor,
he's an outsider.
And besides,
he's only a student!
[ALEXIS] If he was friends with
Kurisu, he's hardly an outsider.
We should feel grateful
they knew each other
and embrace this opportunity.
You'll have to forgive me,
but I'm not following
any of this.
Introduce me to who?
It's not a real person.
He means... Amadeus.
[OKABE] Oh. From your
demonstration earlier.
[MAHO]
That was a version of the system
created using my
sampled memories.
But it's not the only one.
We have data from
another researcher.
Wait, another... [gasps]
[OKABE] Amadeus is storing
Kurisu's memories, too?
[ALEXIS] Up until now,
Maho and I have been
the only ones to speak to her,
gauging her functionality,
but our conversations
are beginning to run dry.
So what do you say?
[MAHO]
I'd suggest you think it over.
[MAHO] I don't know what your
relationship with Kurisu
was like, but...
The closer the two of
you were to each other,
the harder it will be for
you to meet her as Amadeus.
[OKABE] They're her memories
from nine months ago.
[MAHO]
Hello again.
We're planning to start
a new research organization
made up of neuroscientists
from around the world.
Unfortunately, there's not
much prep room right now.
[OKABE]
Where's the professor?
[MAHO] It's Sunday.
That means he's off.
You came all this way,
but are you sure
you want to do this?
I get the feeling the two of
you were closer than I thought.
It'll be hard.
Amadeus can seem real.
It will sound like her
voice talking to you,
but it's a mimic.
And even knowing that,
it's easy to forget.
She'll seem alive,
like she's on the other side
of the screen talking to you.
Try to remember,
the Amadeus you'll meet
is constructed from memories
collected from Kurisu in March.
She's not the girl
you became friends with.
That person is dead.
I know that sounds harsh,
but that's how it is.
[OKABE]
Right.
[MAHO]
The more you talk with Amadeus,
the more the truth
will eat at you.
You'll realize your
friend is gone forever
and that there's nothing
you can do to change that fact.
I'm well aware.
Coming to terms with
this... is why I'm here.
I see.
[lock beeps]
[MAHO] Go ahead and
have a seat in that chair.
[door closes]
[MAHO]
No peeking at my password.
All yours.
[MAHO]
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I've come this far and now
I'm second-guessing myself.
[MAHO chuckles]
It's still not too late.
Run away while you can.
[OKABE]
That's not very comforting.
[MAHO]
I'm just looking out for you.
Well, then... maybe you should
work on your delivery
and be nicer.
Just like Kurisu, you
lab-obsessed girls are all so--
[MAHO]
So, what?
Uh--I get it.
People who spend all
their time on experiments
sometimes forget
how to interact.
If I'm not mistaken, that sounds
like a slanderous statement.
I should sue you for defamation.
Then I withdraw it.
You can let me buy
you a soda as a truce.
[MAHO laughs]
How cheap.
[AMADEUS]
What's so funny about that...
...ma'am?
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE] It was her.
She was right in front of me.
Right there.
So close.
[OKABE]
It was her voice.
Her face.
Go ahead.
You're Okabe Rintaro.
I see your tag.
I'm Makise Kurisu.
It's a real pleasure.
[MAHO]
Okabe here is a student.
We met after the Amadeus
seminar the other day.
He seemed very interested in the
system, so we invited him over.
[AMADEUS]
Really? For you to do that,
there must be something
very special about him.
Um, so, Okabe?
Huh? Uh--
[MIKASE AI]
Are you interested
because you're a
neuroscientist, as well?
[OKABE gasps]
[MAHO]
His major is different,
but he's proven his talent.
Even the Professor has
been impressed by him.
[MIKASE AI]
Ohh!
[MIKASE AI giggles]
[MIKASE AI]
Psst! Ma'am.
[MAHO]
Hmm?
[MIKASE AI]
Could you scoot a little closer
to the speaker for a second?
Huh?
[MIKASE AI]
Please, just do it. Come on!
[MAHO groans]
Bossy avatar.
Could it be that...
[MAHO] Huh?! You've
gotta be kidding me!
[MIKASE AI] You don't have
to be embarrassed about it.
I'm gonna program you to stop
asking crazy things like that!
What was her question?
[MAHO]
Just forget about it!
Uh, yeah, sure. Okay.
[MAHO] You don't say another
childish word, got it?
We didn't bring Okabe here
to talk about absurd
imaginings without any basis.
[MIKASE AI] The more you evade,
the more suspicious you are.
[MAHO]
I'll upload a virus.
[MIKASE AI gasps]
Just kidding! I'll drop it.
Stupid AI.
This is one of the many bugs
we're facing with Amadeus.
Sorry about that.
Feel free to have a
conversation if you like.
[OKABE]
Sure.
[MIKASE AI]
Please forgive me.
You can ask me about
anything and everything.
I'll answer as much
as I am able to.
Anything, huh?
Do you think one...
could construct a time machine?
A time machine? Really?
Yes.
[MIKASE AI]
Well, uh...
This is your question?
Why ask about something
like that? How odd.
[OKABE]
It's a thought experiment.
Huh.
Interesting.
My personal belief is no,
time machines aren't possible.
However, that isn't to say that
they're altogether impossible.
[OKABE gasps]
My belief is that
time machines--
You don't think it's all
just a bunch of nonsense?
[MIKASE AI] It would be
rather hasty to assume that.
[OKABE] There are a number
of time travel theories,
but they're nothing
but speculation.
All of them are unrealistic.
Even so, we could be missing
that one critical discovery
that unlocks a new
understanding, don't you think?
[OKABE] So they're not
possible at the moment,
but... that's not to say
they won't be in the future.
[MIKASE AI]
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
How's that?
The answer she gave me just now
was somewhat different than
when I spoke to her before.
Oh.
[OKABE] Could it be
these changes are due to
the differences in the
alpha and beta world lines?
[door beeps, opens]
Rintaro! Hello, friend.
Or should I say
"konnichiwa"? [laughs]
And the American way's,
uh, "What up, dawg"?
[ALEXIS]
What?
[AMADEUS]
Oof. Now that was embarrassing.
[OKABE gasps]
Don't you start, Christina!
Who's Christina?
[OKABE sputters]
Uh, no one.
Just... forget the name.
[MIKASE AI]
But now I'm curious.
It was an accident, so drop it!
[MIKASE AI] You're clearly very
worked up about something.
Is Christina--
[OKABE] Why must you be
so difficult, Christin--
I mean, Kurisu.
[MAHO] Why do you
keep calling her that?
Don't you start piling
on top of me, too.
[MIKASE AI]
Answer me.
Mute yourself.
Oh, wow, now I
really wanna know.
[ALEXIS laughs]
Our Amadeus is pretty
amazing, eh, Rintaro?
[OKABE]
A tester?
[ALEXIS] Yes. We want
you to talk to Amadeus
from time to time, so we
can expand our data set.
You'll be able to do so
until I return to America.
All we ask is that you visit
us here at the institute
twice a month to
submit your findings.
You want me writing reports?
[ALEXIS] Nothing too formal.
It shouldn't be much trouble.
You can talk with her
whenever you feel like it
and give us your
honest reactions
as to how the system is working.
With Kurisu...
[ALEXIS] If you're not up to the
task, don't hesitate to decline.
I can completely understand
if it's too heartbreaking
to speak to an AI created with
the likeness and personality
of your deceased friend.
[OKABE]
I'll do it.
[MAHO]
Are you sure about this?
We're already getting to
the point where you and I are
running out of new things
to talk to her about.
Plus, I'm quite curious to
see if this changes Amadeus.
How will she react to conversing
with someone on the outside?
[MAHO] Somehow,
I knew this was gonna happen.
Did you now?
[MAHO]
Yes.
From the moment I found out
that he knew Kurisu.
[MIKASE AI] Okabe Rintaro,
I hope we meet again.
[MAHO]
There's somebody out there
who knows a Kurisu I don't.
[MAKISE]
Ma'am. Excuse me?
[MAHO]
Hmm?
[MAKISE]
Why don't I grab that for you?
[MAHO] I'm fine.
I don't need anybody's help!
[MAKISE chuckles]
There's no need to be stubborn.
[MAHO groans]
Here.
[AMADEUS]
Ma'am?
You really need to
watch the tone you take
around this new person.
Why is that?
[MIKASE AI]
He could find it unattractive.
I told you to stop
bringing up foolish things.
[MIKASE AI] But this might
be the last chance you have
at love in your l--
You're the only one who
needs to learn some manners.
[OKABE]
An operation?
Yup! Daru and I thought of it.
A big, festive operation
to cheer up Suzu!
Uh, what exactly are
we talking about here?
To be honest, Suzu actually
scares me a little bit,
but I think she's really
a nice person at heart.
Sometimes when I'm half
asleep, she tiptoes over
--[phone buzzing]
--and puts a blanket on me.
And she's always helping
Ruka and the others
with whatever they
have going on.
[OKABE gasps]
[MAYURI]
Are you okay?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
[MAYURI] So we're thinking of
throwing Suzu a Christmas party
as a present to help brighten up
her day. Doesn't that sound fun?
A party, huh?
Are you busy?
It's not that I'm busy.
I just doubt Suzuha
would want me there.
I'd probably just upset her.
I don't think
that's true, though.
Suzu wants to patch
things up with you
and be friends again.
I'm positive.
--[phone buzzing]
--[gasps]
[MAYURI] You should
answer whoever's calling.
I'll wait for you
right here in the park.
I'll be quick.
[AMADEUS sighs] I see you
finally decided to pick up
after ignoring my calls
eight times in a row.
[OKABE]
Well, I was busy.
[AMADEUS] If you don't
feel like talking to me,
I suppose it can't be helped.
[scoffs] It's just...
with you being a tester,
I thought I'd get to chat with
more people than I used to.
[OKABE] That's her. I know that
spunk and that moodiness...
The fierce curiosity
driving her...
The refusal to lose.
[AMADEUS] Why aren't you
saying anything? In any case,
you can call me whenever
you feel like it, I guess.
But I'm a busy person, too,
so I might not be
able to answer you.
[OKABE]
Without a doubt...
It's Makise Kurisu.