[STREET FOLK chattering]
[OKABE]
Seriously?
World War III?
[SUZUHA] Let me put it
into perspective for you:
that's upwards of 5.7
billion human lives
snuffed out by the year 2036.
And it all starts with this.
[MAYURI]
But what is "this"?
[DARU]
Totally a mech.
Please tell me it transforms.
It's a time machine, Daru.
--Huh?
--[DARU] Sorry?
You're familiar with it.
That's good, Uncle. Very good.
I can get to the point.
We're gonna run interference.
Uh--
I refuse.
[BOTH gasp]
Okarin.
[OKABE] I've been jumping
from world line to world line
for weeks.
I've run interference--
so many times I'm
barely myself anymore.
The only way I was able to
land back onto this world line
was by allowing Kurisu to die.
And now you're asking me
to go another round?
I refuse!
What are you talking about?
Kurisu?
Oh!
You mean the scientist chick who
got, like, stabbed or whatever
at the Radio Building
the other day?
Rintarou. Hear me out.
What if I told you the
circumstances of her death
on the afternoon
of July 28th, 2010
play directly into what
kicked off the war?
That the reason I'm here
is to see to it she survives?
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
I'm listening.
I don't have a clue
how it all dovetails.
All I know is I've
been entrusted
with an important mission:
rescue Makise Kurisu and
shift things to a world line
beyond the divergence barrier,
free of the attractor field.
A little place we
call Stei's Gate.
[OKABE]
I don't believe it.
You actually hatched
this plan yourself.
By that I mean you will.
With Dad.
Though you're the first to
admit it's pure conjecture.
Push comes to shove,
it's possible this is
all wishful thinking.
Even if a Steins Gate
world line exists,
the odds of us reaching
one are slim to none.
Odds be damned,
though. I'm all in.
As you always like to remind us:
nothing ventured,
nothing gained, right?
If a future without World War
III is worth the risk to you,
take my hand.
[MAYURI]
Um... Okay, to be honest,
I don't think I understood very
much of what just got said.
But...
This friend of yours--
This Makise Kurisu?
Sounds to me like she's worth
taking a chance, right?
I say you should go for it!
[DARU] Face it, chief.
It's your cuppa tea.
All this World War III
stuff seems, well,
no offense, you understand,
but tailor-made for your
special brand of crazy.
[OKABE]
I do this for her. No one else.
Got it?
Whatever gets you there.
[DARU chuckles]
Climb aboard!
[OKABE]
It can actually carry two?
[SUZUHA]
Well, yeah.
Like this puppy's inventor
would've have skimped on
installing a backseat?
Huh? Uh...
[MAYURI]
Be careful.
[SUZUHA]
Leave your cell phone here.
We'd all be screwed
five ways from Tuesday
if it crossed signals
with the one
your past self'll be carrying.
Watch it for me?
[MAYURI]
Mm.
Good luck, guys.
Nice, uh, set up you got.
Thanks. Works like a charm.
I've already stopped
off at 1975 and 2000.
She's running low on fuel,
though. That's the thing.
You've got to watch the
indicators like a hawk.
[gasps] Wait. So we can not
only go backward in time,
but forward?
Uh--I should hope so.
What the in hell'd be
the point if we couldn't?
[OKABE]
I see. This one must come from
a different world
line than its twin.
[SUZUHA]
Have a seat.
I'm setting coordinates for the
day of, just shy of 12 o'clock.
I don't dare go back any further
because I can't
change our position.
If we stir up trouble
at the Radio Building,
it might throw Kurisu's
movements out of whack.
We're about to pull an
ungodly amount of Gs here,
so you might want to
prepare yourself.
--[hissing]
--[gasps]
Okarin...
[OKABE groans, gasps]
What are these?
[SUZUHA]
They come with the territory.
Little beads of time.
Kinda pretty, huh?
[SUZUHA]
Come on.
[OKABE]
Sorry, I, uh--
I just need to let my
stomach settle a bit.
[SUZUHA]
Ugh. Somebody's a wuss.
Hurry it up!
'Kay, critical point:
avoid running into your
past self at all costs.
We could have a major paradox
on our hands otherwise.
How long do you
think this'll take?
Uh, well...maybe 20
minutes, give or take?
All right, I'm gonna stay here
and prep the time machine
for our return trip, and you do
what you can to save Makise.
[OKABE]
Wish me luck.
July 28th.
The day I found Kurisu on the
floor, soaked in her own blood.
Mayuri and I had come to
see Dr. Nakabachi's lecture
and were waiting for it to start
when we heard a
sound on the roof.
[gasps]
[OKABE exhales]
[OKABE]
That's right.
This must be when Mayuri
heads to the vending machines
on the 7th floor.
[OKABE]
Is anything not an emergency?
[MAYURI]
I'm sorry.
I know sometimes it's not,
but this one counts for sure.
[OKABE]
Better play it safe.
I'll take the far
stairs back to eight.
I don't believe it!
A metal Oopa!
[OKABE]
And that's good?
Uh-huh! You bet it is!
[OKABE pants]
Should be safe now.
--[footsteps]
--[OKABE gasps]
Uh--oh, I'm sorry.
Ku-Kurisu.
[MAKISE]
Um, have we met before?
[OKABE]
No. This is too much.
I don't think I know you, do I?
[OKABE]
Kurisu.
Look, whoever--[gasps]
[MAKISE]
What is your trauma?
Don't rush to
help me or anything.
[OKABE gasping]
I, uh...
Uh--
I'm just... here to see...
[FEMALE ANNOUNCEMENT]
Your attention, please.
Doctor Nakabachi's conference
is about to begin
on the 8th floor lecture hall.
All who are interested
are welcome...
[MAKISE]
At least finish a sentence!
[MAKISE sighs]
[NAKABACHI] Printed on the
handouts there in front of you
is more or less
the hard blueprint
for one of mankind's
oldest ambitions.
Of course, the
theoretical scaffolding
begs some explanation.
[NAKABACHI]
As I'm sure you're aware,
mainstream science currently...
[SUZUHA]
In the brief I was given,
they said you'd be able
to pick her out instantly.
Is that true?
[OKABE]
Yeah.
[SUZUHA]
Right. Bear in mind, though.
It's probably a bad idea
to take her off site.
We don't know who
kills her or why.
And in the event
that her death is
a fixed point on the timeline,
we don't want things
getting more complicated.
I learned that the
hard way with Mayuri.
--[OKABE] Doctor!
--[OKABE gasps]
[NAKABACHI]
Save your questions unt--
[OKABE]
I have none, sir!
I throw down the gauntlet as
to your "theory's" authorship!
Do you take us all for
babes in the wilderness?
Please. World lines?
Kerr Black...
[OKABE] Any moment now,
this is where she'll end up.
What on earth am I gonna do?
[gasps] Wait!
What if she's killed somewhere
else and dragged here?
Damn it! I hadn't
thought of that!
[footsteps]
[OKABE gasps]
[OKABE]
There she is.
This is where it happens.
[OKABE]
What is that she's reading?
Time machines?
Is that why so much
is riding on this?
--[footsteps]
--[MAKISE] Uh--
[NAKABACHI]
Stupid kids.
[MAKISE gasps]
What in the hell do you want?
Look, please.
I just want you to
read this, 'kay, Dad?
[OKABE]
"Dad"?
[OKABE gasps]
Nakabachi's her dad?!
Look, I... I'm just trying
to bury the hatchet.
It's been years. Too damn long.
I want you in my life again.
[OKABE] Don't tell me
her father's the one who--
[MAKISE] ...as you
like to say, and well,
I'm now convinced that
you were right all along.
I wanted your opinion
on the theory.
If this paper gets accepted,
you can lord it over
all the stuffed shirts
who laughed you
out of the academy.
[NAKABACHI gasps]
I did not get "laughed out"!
I turned my back
on their politics
to pursue my
researches unfettered!
[MAKISE]
Sorry.
[NAKABACHI]
Hmph.
This isn't half bad.
[MAKISE]
Really?
'Cause I was thinking, maybe,
if you were okay with the idea,
we could publish it
under both of our names.
I mean, after all,
you're the one who
inspired me to--
[NAKABACHI]
Don't be ridiculous.
Go home.
[MAKISE]
What?
[NAKABACHI] If this paper
sees the light of day,
it'll do so under my name.
[MAKISE]
Uh--excuse me?
That's called stealing!
I knew you could be cruel,
but I never thought
you'd stoop to--
[NAKABACHI]
Shut up!
--[MAKISE groans]
--[OKABE gasps]
[gasps, groans]
[NAKABACHI]
You dare call me a thief?
[gasps]
--[MAKISE gasps]
--[NAKABACHI grunts]
Bitch! What makes you think
you're so much better than me?
A daughter's got no goddamn
right to outshine her father!
Every second you're out there
whoring to make a
name for yourself,
you trample my reputation
as a genius of the age!
--[OKABE yells]
--[NAKABACHI gasps, groans]
[coughs, gasps]
[OKABE panting]
You were my heckler,
weren't you?
Heh. I see.
You were in cahoots to make
nattering ol' Nakabachi
shit the bed during
what should've been
his moment of glory.
[NAKABACHI laughs]
Well, you succeeded.
But success comes at a price.
Dad, no!
[OKABE]
Stand your ground. Protect her!
[NAKABACHI growls]
Where's your heckling now?
Come on, let's hear it!
[gasps]
[NAKABACHI groans]
[gasps, grunts]
Son of bitch!
[NAKABACHI grunts, chuckles]
[MAKISE]
Dad, this is crazy!
Please stop!
So I'm crazy?
I'll show you crazy!
Look out!
[gasps]
[NAKABACHI yells, grunts]
You're an idiot!
A DNA fluke!
You're not as smart as me!
My name belongs in
the annals of history.
[grunts] You're nothing!
Daddy, please.
[NAKABACHI]
If it hadn't been for you,
I wouldn't be the academic
laughing stock I am now!
--[NAKABACHI grunting]
--[MAKISE groaning]
--Stop!
--[gasps, grunts]
--[NAKABACHI gasps]
--Stop!
[thud]
[OKABE gasping]
Oh, god.
--[MAKISE groaning]
--[OKABE gasping]
[OKABE]
Oh, my god!
[laughs]
Look at that.
Poetic justice
all around, I'd say.
--[footsteps]
--[NAKABACHI laughing]
--[gasps]
--[MAKISE] I'm sorry.
I didn't mean...
[OKABE]
What?
[MAKISE] I didn't mean
to drag you into this.
I just wanted him to...
To acknowledge me.
Kurisu...
[MAKISE wheezing]
[MAKISE]
I'm so scared. I...
I don't... want to die.
I'm not ready.
[MAKISE crying]
This wasn't...
Wasn't supposed to...
[OKABE gasps]
No. Oh, god!
[OKABE]
Please no!
[OKABE sobbing]
[screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
[MAYURI]
Neat-o! They're already back!
Okarin!
--[MAYURI gasps]
--Whoa. Dude!
--[OKABE mumbling]
--What the hell happened to you?
--He's gonna be all right.
It's just a little
bit complicated.
I'm responsible for her death.
I did it.
I'm the one to blame.
Her blood is on my hands.
I'm responsible for her death.
I'm responsible...
[MAYURI]
Okarin.
Walk it off. Look,
I know you're in shock,
but you've got to
pick yourself up.
We've got enough fuel
for one more trip
and now we know how
things play out, so--
[OKABE]
Shut up!
I won't do it!
I won't put myself
through that again!
The attractor field convergence
will cause Kurisu's death
no matter what I do.
I can't.
[OKABE]
It's all...
All my fault.
[SUZUHA]
The lives of 5.7 billion people
are at stake here.
If you save Makise Kurisu,
you save every one of them.
I can't do it.
[SUZUHA]
That is not true.
You can at least
try more than once!
[OKABE]
Once?
Are you mad?
I tried dozens of times!
No, double--triple that!
And every time, I failed!
[OKABE]
I know how cruel time can be.
You may not think that's true,
but believe me, I do.
We like to imagine we can bend
it to suit us, when really--
[OKABE]
Really...
This was bound to happen.
It was stupid of me
to play along.
I'm sorry, but...
I'm just done.
Let time have its way.
No! If I have to slap some sense
into you, I'll be happy to--
[MAYURI]
Please, stop it!
It isn't fair for you
to force him like this!
--[gasps]
--[OKABE sobbing]
[SUZUHA]
But at this rate,
we won't be able to
change the future!
[MAYURI]
And why?
Why does Okarin have to carry
the weight of the future
all by himself?
It's too much for him.
[SUZUHA] Because Uncle
Okarin has an ability
that lets him observe and
remember the world lines.
[MAYURI] But Okarin never
asked for that responsibility.
Look what it's done to him.
If he tries again, he's only
going to end up hurt more.
[MAYURI] Besides,
it's probably impossible
for one person to change
the future, anyway.
[OKABE]
I'm sorry... Kurisu...
Kuri...
[OKABE sobbing]
[MAYURI]
Hey, Okarin?
[OKABE sobbing]
[MAYURI] You don't have to
push yourself so hard anymore.
And it's okay to cry.
Really.
[MAYURI]
Because I'm here.
I've got you.
[MAKISE]
Okabe.
Jeez, seriously.
You're nothing but trouble,
you know that?
Give it here. I keep
a sewing kit on me.
I can get it fixed up
for you in a jiff.
Okabe!
As you've probably noticed,
it's kinda dark in here,
so don't expect needlework
worthy of Athena.
Okabe.
I'd say what color thread I'm
using, 'cept I can't even tell.
[cicadas singing]
[MAKISE]
Jeez, seriously.
Okabe?
...you know that?
Give it here. I keep
a sewing kit on me.
I can get it fixed up
for you in a jiff.
As you've probably noticed,
it's kinda dark in here,
so don't expect needlework...
Okabe.
I'd say what color thread I'm
using, 'cept I can't even tell.
[MAKISE]
Okabe.
...seriously. You're nothing
but trouble, you know that?
Give it here. I keep a sewing...
Okabe.
...get it fixed up
for you in a jiff.
As you've probably noticed,
it's kinda dark in here,
so don't expect needlework
worthy of Athena.
I'd say what color thread I'm
using, 'cept I can't even tell.
Jeez, seriously.
Okabe?
...you know that?
Give it here. I keep a
sewing kit on me. I can...
Okabe!
...in a jiff.
As you've probably noticed,
it's kinda dark in here...
Okabe!
...worthy of Athena.
I'd say what color thread I'm
using, 'cept I can't even tell.
[MAYURI]
The cicadas have all gone away.
[OKABE] It's been a while
since I've been to this park.
Yeah. It sounds to me like
you've been super busy
ever since summer break ended.
[OKABE chuckles]
Actually, the other day
I went on my first group date.
You did?
--[cell phone vibrates]
--[OKABE chuckles]
Ah. Speak of the devil.
Hey, what's up?
Yeah? Tomorrow?
Sure. Maybe.
Let me guess.
You need a guy to
even out the numbers.
Right?
[chuckles]
Whatever.
I'll be there.
See you.
Turns out college life is busier
than I expected. [chuckles]
[MAYURI]
It's been too long.
[MAYURI] But seeing Okarin
again... makes me feel so happy.
Hey. Wait up.
[MAYURI] Will you stop
in the lab sometime?
You haven't been by in forever
and it's been so
quiet without you.
Yeah, I will.
That's a promise, okay?
Sure. See you around.
[MAYURI]
Yup!
[OKABE]
Mayuri is fine.
Still alive.
The city? Remains.
And me?
Nothing has changed.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Makise Kurisu.
It's a pleasure.
[OKABE gasps]
Kurisu.
Kurisu...
Kurisu... Kurisu... Kurisu...
Is this how fate intends
our paths to converge?
Well? Hououin Kyouma?
[OKABE] After everything
that's happened--
the horrors I've gone through.
I have to do it after all.
[OKABE]
El Psy Congroo.