[MAHO]
Okabe?
What are you doing
here so early?
Hiyajo, listen.
I have a question for you.
Yeah, what?
Have you forsaken your silly
mad-scientist voice?
[OKABE] Our D-RINE worked,
and Amadeus was lost,
but we still met Hiyajo.
Apparently under very
different circumstances.
[inaudible]
[OKABE] Even as the world
lines keep changing,
our connections remain constant,
as if the conditions
reshape themselves
to support the
relationships we've built.
[phone vibrates]
[OKABE]
Hey, Mayuri.
[MAYURI]
Hello? You there? It's Suzuha.
She's in some major trouble!
[OKABE]
Suzuha?
[MAYURI]
Yeah!
She's about to get
in the time machine
to go back one year
into the past!
She's leaving, even though
she can't come back!
Damn it all, why?
[MAYURI]
What?
Why'd you have to
make the choice
to talk to me about it, huh?
There's not enough time.
I can't even investigate
the situation
and find out exactly
what's changed.
There's only one element
that matters now:
They must leave
in the time machine.
[OKABE]
Kagari?
She's way too early!
What's this about?
[OKABE] Kagari's still going
after the time machine.
Which means I've
gotta find her,
and stop her in her tracks.
[ALEXIS]
Rintaro.
[ALEXIS] What business
could you possibly have
in a place like this?
You know my suspicion?
I think you know far more
about the time machine
than I gave you credit for.
Is my assessment correct?
[ALEXIS]
Where's Kagari?
I know after she
escaped the facility
that she met up with you
and your little lab crew,
so don't even try denying it.
You can't fool me. How much
of the truth do you know?
[OKABE]
I see.
Things are different because
the D-RINE erased Amadeus.
Is it possible that
the professor
wasn't able to
fully brainwash Kagari?
[OKABE grunts]
If that's true...
Professor Leskinen.
You're right.
I know things about the future
that you couldn't
begin to imagine.
Would you like to hear
about them?
[OKABE]
I'll tell you everything.
Moeka!
[gunshot]
--[OKABE groans]
--[MOEKA] Huh?
[MOEKA]
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine,
it's just a scratch.
You need help!
[OKABE]
There's no time for that!
I need your help now.
As lab member 005!
Kiryu Moeka!
[whimpering]
[REYES]
Please, don't do this!
Kaga--
Kagari.
[KAGARI] I won't allow
the past to be changed.
I will not let anyone erase
the day that I met Mommy.
Nobody's getting it.
I'll destroy the time machine.
Suzuha. Is that really Kagari?
But, why?
[KAGARI]
Mommy Mayuri.
Are you a part of all of this?
Do you wanna change
the future, too,
just like Suzuha has been
trying to do for so many years?
Do you wanna make it so
that you and I never meet,
and you don't become my mom?
No, it's not that at all.
[KAGARI] Because that's
the last thing I want!
However terrible the future
might be... I don't even care!
It's the only reality I want.
I won't let you change it!
[gasps]
What's the matter, Kagari?
You afraid to do it?
I will shoot!
[MAYURI]
Kagari, please.
Stop. Let her go.
It's dangerous, Mommy,
stay back! I can't let her go.
I have to do this!
[gasps]
No, Mayuri!
Please, get back!
Oh my goodness.
That was scary.
I just realized I was holding
my breath the entire time!
I'm just grateful it worked,
and that you both decided
not to shoot each other.
--Mommy? But I...
--Listen.
Don't be sad.
You see, even though I am
getting in the time machine,
and I'm going back
into the past with Suzuha,
I'm only doing this
to make someone special
to me see the light.
It's not gonna work!
No matter what you both do,
or how hard you try,
nothing ever works!
No good can come of it!
It will only keep us apart!
There's only enough fuel
left to go one way!
You won't be able to come back!
What'll happen to you? I don't
even want to think about it.
[MAYURI]
I understand.
This might be reckless,
and it could be hopeless, too.
But still, it's worth
it for Okarin.
He has a special power
to change the future.
Well, no.
I think we all have
that same power,
but he's learned to use it
in a different way
to guide us to
the best future possible.
Which is why I'm going,
to give him that extra little
push he needs to go back
and change something important.
And if that's all it takes,
I know I can do it.
It's the only thing I can do.
Orihime's gift to Hikoboshi.
Hikoboshi? But wait.
[MAYURI] If my Hikoboshi had
burned bright just once more,
it might've changed
everything for us.
He's Mommy's... Hikoboshi?
[SUZUHA] Kagari, why don't
you come with us?
[KAGARI gasps]
Come back into the past with us.
We can change the future!
The world doesn't have to
fall apart or be sad,
and no one you love
has to die, either!
We can create a beautiful,
bright future instead,
one where everyone
can be happy together!
[MAYURI]
Well, then? Come on, Kagari.
Let's be together!
Really?
[OKABE]
Do it for my sake, too!
[MAYURI]
Okarin? And Moeka?
[SUZUHA]
What are you doing here?
Listen. I came to this
time from the future.
[ALL gasp]
[OKABE] I did it using
the time leap machine.
This place is about
to become a war zone.
You don't have very long.
You have to get in and go, now!
[KAGARI] That can't be! The
professor shouldn't even know--
Leskinen is currently
unconscious in the stairwell.
But it's only a matter of time.
You'll let us leave?
[gasps]
Now, Lab Member 002,
Shiina Mayuri!
Please, make Operation
Arclight a success!
And when I'm mired
in self-pity,
knock some sense into me, huh?
[gasps]
'Kay! I promise I will!
Come on, Kagari. Let's go!
[KAGARI]
Mommy.
[gunfire]
Moeka!
I can't hold them long.
Hurry up!
You have to come now, Kagari!
Mommy. I...
[KAGARI]
Okarin.
Are you certain?
You're okay with never
seeing Mommy again?
Won't that break your heart?
What are you blabbering about?
Mayuri is my precious
hostage, you know.
No matter where or when
she may venture,
I will always bring her back!
[chuckles]
[SUZUHA]
Kagari!
Aren't you coming?
Go! They won't get anywhere
near you! I'll protect you!
But, Kagari!
[KAGARI]
Hurry! Leave!
Mayuri, let's go!
Get in!
[KAGARI]
You're Mommy's Hikoboshi!
I'm trusting you.
I choose to, because you said
I can be with Mommy again.
That's a promise!
[inaudible]
[OKABE]
It showed up after all.
Okabe, no!
Mommy!
[OKABE]
I understand.
[OKABE] This time...
there's nothing to fear!
[OKABE]
This is it. This moment!
[OKABE laughing]
Attend me well,
for I won't suffer fools!
Schrodinger's box
has shattered wide open!
The time machine you bastards
sought no longer exists!
It has traveled
through space-time
and dissolved into the ether
along with your schemes!
Writhe with anguish. Tremble
in fear, for you should!
I, Hououin Kyouma, will prevail
against you and your designs.
Indeed, fate itself
will kneel at my feet!
Nothing will deter me.
I'll find Steins Gate!
Do you hear?
For that...
[OKABE chuckling]
...is what I have chosen!
[OKABE grunts]
[MAYURI]
Huh? What's that?
[DARU]
Hold up.
Are there two time machines?
[gasps]
[MAYURI]
A call from myself?
[DARU]
Huh?
What's going on?
[MAYURI]
I guess I'll answer it.
Uh, hello?
Who's this?
Please, don't be afraid,
I need you to hear me out.
[MAYURI gasps]
Do you love Hououin Kyouma?
Truly?
Exactly one minute
from right now,
Okarin will come back
from the past.
But he didn't succeed
in saving Makise Kurisu.
[MAYURI gasps]
[MAYURI]
So that means...
...no matter what it takes,
you're going to have to
confront your Hikoboshi.
You're the only one
who can open his eyes.
My Hikoboshi?
[gasps]
[MAYURI]
Yes.
[BOTH]
Hououin Kyouma.
Okarin's heart will
be shattered,
but you can get him
on his feet again.
It's gonna take more than just
speaking his name, though.
Thirty seconds to go!
[MAYURI]
Think of the exact moment
Hououin Kyouma came into being,
do you remember that?
[gasps]
[MAYURI]
The moment he came into being?
Yes, I remember.
[MAYURI] I'm entrusting
you with 27 years' worth
of love and pain.
You'll have to endure so much.
But I won't stop believing...
...in my Okarin...
...in our friends,
and in myself.
So, please, never
give up hope, either.
Because the rest
is in your hands.
Too-too-roo!
Hold on! I--
Mayuri, it's time!
We have to go!
Please, just tell me!
Does Steins Gate really exist?
[MAYURI]
It does I'm sure of it.
And now the second time
machine's gone, too?
Wait, who was that on the phone?
[alarm blaring]
[SUZUHA]
It's no use, Mayuri.
I'm sorry, but there's
not much hope.
[MAYURI]
I see.
Because there's
no fuel left, right?
If we had stayed, it would've
caused a time paradox,
so we had to jump.
I hate to say it, but this
might be the end for us.
There's no telling what time
we might be shot into.
One year later, or a
million back, I can't say.
[MAYURI]
Thank you, Suzuha.
Why would you thank me?
Thank you so much for letting me
come along with you like this.
And don't worry!
I'm confident the other Mayuri
and my Hikoboshi can take
care of things from here.
I'm so jealous of Uncle
Okarin right now, you know?
If I had Reading
Steiner like him,
then I could remember
everything.
Even when world lines changed.
Like talking to
this version of you,
who is younger than me,
and everything about this time.
It's weird to think I won't talk
to you for another six years.
Wait, even longer.
Unless you happen to start
talking right after you're born!
[laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[MAYURI]
Hey, Okarin.
When the world seems like
it's fallen into darkness...
...and you're afraid of
the shadows all around...
...try not to close your eyes.
Don't ever give up.
And promise you won't let
Hououin Kyouma die.
That way, my feelings
can still reach your heart.
Even if they have to
travel for hundreds,
even thousands of hours,
like the light
of some distant star....
I will wait in the lab,
no matter how long it takes
for you and all the
others to join me.
And when you do,
we'll be together at last.
[MAYURI] I'll see you again
in Steins Gate!
[MAYURI]
Okarin!
[OKABE]
I killed her...
He's gonna be all right.
It's just a little bit
complicated.
[MAYURI]
Okarin.
[phone vibrating]
Okarin, it's your phone.
[DARU]
A text?
[SUZUHA]
Open it.
[MAYURI]
I shouldn't.
[SUZUHA]
Just do it.
[OKABE]
I'm responsible for her death.
I'm responsible...
[MAYURI]
It says to turn on the news.
[DARU]
Seriously?
[REPORTER]
Despite the cargo bay fire,
Doctor Nakabachi's plane
managed to land safely
within the borders
of the former Soviet Union,
to which he'd recently defected.
--[DARU] 'Kay, that's weird.
--[MAYURI] That's my metal oopa!
[MAYURI]
I know it is!
[DARU]
Why's it in Russia?
[SUZUHA]
That thesis of his.
That's what starts
World War III.
It basically sparks
an arms race,
only the goal is which country
can build a time machine first.
Take first place
and win the world.
That's how it starts, but things
get hostile pretty quick.
The lives of 5.7 billion
people are at stake here.
Save Makise Kurisu and
you save every one of them.
I can't do it.
Things'll end up just
as they did with Mayuri.
No matter what I did, she died.
[MAYURI]
Think of the exact moment
Hououin Kyouma came into being!
Do you remember that?
[OKABE]
Believe me, I know.
You may not think I do,
but I know how
cruel time can be.
We like to imagine we can
bend it to suit us, but...
...this was bound to happen.
It was stupid of me
to play along.
I'm sorry, but I'm...
...I'm just done.
Let time have its way.
[gasps]
[inaudible]
[OKABE]
Hail and well met...
...old friend.
That you're able to open
this means you've seen it.
You've seen firsthand
what became of Makise
and failed to prevent it.
I feel for you.
Believe me, I do.
That said, the pain you're going
through right now is necessary.
I daren't deny you--us...
the bitter inspiration
it represents.
Without it, you cannot hope
to carve out your destiny.
Now we can marshal
our resources properly.
I hereby charge you with the
task of reaching Steins Gate.
The target world line's
charming little nickname
comes care of me as well,
which is to say,
it comes from you.
Care to guess its significance?
Bingo. There's none.
[MAHO]
Hey, are you sure about this?
[DARU]
Yeah, for the most part.
[MAHO] Don't you think
the Okabe in 2010
will be humiliated
by the whole thing?
No need to worry about that.
He was even more
incredible back then.
Just thinking about it
makes me shudder.
[OKABE] And to further
please our whimsy,
Operation Skuld will be the name
we assign to this mission.
Forge of yesterday whatever
you must to save the future.
Deceive yourself
in every last detail.
Deceive the world.
Do this, and victory is assured.
Best of luck to you, old friend.
El. Psy. Congroo.
[FARIS]
Cut!
Nice job! You nailed it! Meow!
[OKABE]
Now the final step.
We have to send the video
in a D-mail to the past.
Ruka.
On it.
The video that you just made
goes to Kyouma in 2010,
and the one Hashida
already filmed,
that goes to Suzuha in 2011,
right after you depart on
your trip, is that right?
[MAHO]
You really wanna do this?
[OKABE]
Yes, why?
Because you'll be manning
the inaugural run
of an experimental time machine.
[MAHO] You've told me you're
supposed to die in 2025,
I get that,
but it doesn't mean it's okay
for you to just throw your--
[OKABE] I have no intention
of doing anything of the sort.
I fully believe our efforts
here will pay off.
Yeah, but...
What if you interpret
it differently?
In 2025, Okabe Rintaro doesn't
perish like we thought.
Instead, he boards the first
version of our time machine
and departs for another
corner of space-time.
If I were to disappear from
this world line, well, then...
...that's essentially
the same as dying here.
Wouldn't you agree?
[MAHO] I'd call that mindset
overly optimistic.
[OKABE] Emotions aside,
it's a viable theory, is it not?
[chuckles]
[OKABE]
The world can be deceived.
My friends! I thank you for
following my lead until now!
As you know... on that
day, in the year 2011,
a time machine departed
for the past and was lost.
I venture into the abyss
to find Mayuri and Suzuha.
With the Kerr black hole tracer,
I'll be able to home
in on their locus.
With luck, it will lead me
straight to where they are.
[KAGARI]
Okarin.
[KAGURI]
Take this.
[OKABE]
Are you sure?
I am. Please give it to Mommy
when you find her, for me.
Yes, I promise.
[MAHO] I just have to
ask you one last time.
About Steins Gate.
Does it exist?
And can we reach it?
[OKABE]
It exists. We'll find it.
As of now, the operation
commences!
Operation Altair!
That is the name by which
it shall be known!
Do you think that he'll succeed?
'Course he will.
If anyone can do it, Kyouma can.
Yeah, I'm with Faris.
He's special.
Nothing's out of his reach.
Exactly right.
Okarin makes the
impossible possible.
Good luck, Okarin.
[MAHO] The universe may not
have a discernible end.
It's infinite,
but it had a beginning.
And as for its component
parts, the stars,
those definitely have a limited
cosmological shelf life.
They're finite.
If history tells us anything,
it's that scientists
often make very poor poets.
We're a ship of fools,
chasing phantoms,
heedless of what
underwrites natural law.
If we could somehow
attain that wisdom,
perhaps it would only plunge
us into madness and ruin.
Humans exceeding
the speed of light?
It's more foolish
than fish attempting
to make a life on land.
And yet...
...these words.
They're meant for those
foolhardy enough
to defy the counsels of fate.
An epigraph for
their obstinance.
[inaudible]
Suzuha!
[laughs]
Did you doubt me, my loves?