[OKABE gasps]
--[MAYURI] Okarin!
--Huh?
[KURISU]
Okabe.
[DARU]
Okarin.
[RUKA]
Okabe.
[FARIS]
Kyouma!
[MOEKA]
Okabe.
[SUZUHA]
Uncle Okarin.
[OKABE]
Splendid!
All my minions are here.
Thus it commences
the 65,536th
roundtable meeting!
[OKABE]
Yes. All my minions.
And yet, it feels
devoid of all life.
So dim. So cold.
It's as if all the bones
in my body
are comprised of steel
or titanium.
[clock ticking]
[gasping]
--[KURISU] Okabe.
--Huh?
[OKABE]
You're here. How is that--?
And I'm not the only one.
Mayuri, too. Hashida, as well.
[OKABE]
Huh?
Thus, as of now,
may the 65,536th
roundtable meeting commence!
[ticking echoes]
[ticking continues]
[OKABE groans]
[OKABE]
Where... Where am I?
My whole body feels... heavy.
[OKABE]
A strange room?
[OKABE grunts]
[OKABE groaning]
[panting]
[OKABE] What happened?
What's wrong with me?
Huh?
[gasps]
[clattering]
I look so old. What the--
Is this really me?
--[beeping]
--[footsteps]
[MAN]
Hello. Barrel Titor speaking.
[panting]
[OKABE]
The last thing I remember
is repeating the time leap.
I should be...
[groans, gasps]
[OKABE]
What the hell?
It's...
[coughing]
[motorcycle engine revving]
[snarling]
[whimpering]
[gasping]
[panting]
[grunts, groans]
[OKABE]
This place is...
It can't be.
Akiba?
I was at the lab.
What could have happened
to the others?
[footsteps]
[SOLDIER 1] Don't move!
What are you doing out here?
Answer me!
This area is strictly
off-limits to civilians!
[SOLDIER 2]
Put your hands above your head.
State your name and ID number.
What?
[gunshot]
[SOLDIER 2] I repeat,
state your name and ID!
I... I, uh.
[SOLDIER 2]
That's it.
--[gunshot]
--[SOLDIER 2 grunts]
[SOLDIER 1 grunts]
--[body thuds]
--[tires squeal]
[gasps]
It's Suzuha!
[footsteps]
[OKABE groans]
[SUZUHA]
Who the hell are you?
Tell me how you know
my name, right now!
[OKABE] I don't--
What are you talking about?
Have you really forgotten me?
State your name, immediately!
It's Okabe!
I'm Okabe Rintaro!
[gasps]
Please!
You're kidding me.
It's really you?
But that's impossible!
[engine revving]
--[OKABE gasps]
--[SUZUHA] Hmm.
[MAN]
Moe Moe, baby.
Kiss-kiss, bang-bang.
[locks disengage,
mechanical whirring]
[SUZUHA]
This way.
[MAN] So, you finally decided
to wake up, huh?
Hi, old friend.
[footsteps]
[MAN]
You don't recognize me?
What if I talk more
like I did back then?
Your banana's
all squishy, Okarin.
[gasping]
[OKABE]
Daru.
--Is that really you?
--Come on, man.
How could anybody
ever forget a stud like me,
ya freakin' noob?
Right, lovely daughter?
Did you forget you dropped
half your body weight, Dad?
Even so, my dashing good looks
and charisma haven't gone away.
[SUZUHA] Yeah, yeah, just keep
tellin' yourself that.
Daru. I need to know something.
Please tell me.
What year are we in right now?
[DARU]
It's 2036.
The world you knew is gone.
Devolved into pure chaos.
[OKABE]
This is 2036?
[DARU]
Hard to believe?
[OKABE] No. All I have
left is believing.
It's been 25 years now.
You and I are
crusty old geezers.
But that doesn't make sense.
I thought that in 2025,
I was supposed to--
That's what I don't get, either.
How can Uncle Okarin
be alive and somewhat well?
You always told me that he
had died years ago, Dad.
Just so we're clear,
I never lied.
He was dead.
And that is the truth.
How far back can you remember?
What's the last thing?
Let me see.
I was using the time
leap machine
to go back into the past
in order to try to save Mayuri.
But then, when I came to,
I was here.
Interesting.
I remember the time
leap machine acting up that day.
[gasps]
[DARU] We don't even know
the exact reason for it.
All we could determine
was the thing had failed us.
And so, in order to get back
to that period,
we had to exceed
the 48 hour limit.
Meanwhile, the world
descended into chaos
as the great powers fought
over the time travel theory.
Are you telling me...
...that Mayuri was killed?
Well, all we know for sure
is that Mayushii disappeared.
And, then, a few years
after that happened,
we decided to build the time
machine all by ourselves.
That's what began it.
What we now call Valkyrie.
Is that a code name?
[DARU] Yes, and that
started something else.
Our war against
the rest of the world.
[OKABE]
Meaning what?
You already
know what that means.
Every world power,
racing toward time travel.
They believed Kurisu's
theory to be closest.
And that those
with her knowledge
would complete it first.
Namely, Okabe Rintaro,
along with his organization,
known as Valkyrie.
Everyone on our team
became prey,
hunted down by operatives
from all corners of the globe.
Then came that bleak day
in 2025.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[OKABE] Daru, I've got
some terrible news.
[DARU]
What? Did something happen?
[OKABE] It appears I've
walked into Stratfor's trap.
[DARU] For real? Well, get out!
Make your way here!
--[OKABE] I can't.
--[DARU gasps]
[OKABE] I won't do anything
to jeopardize
the safety
of the other members.
[OKABE]
Listen my friend. Thank you.
Back in the day,
you encouraged me
to keep going when I
was about to break.
And Daru, know that
I'm counting on you.
Finish the machine.
Okarin?
[OKABE] From now on,
it's in your hands.
Wait. Don't hang up!
[SUZUHA]
After that, you were gone.
You fell into
Stratfor's clutches.
And they tortured
you relentlessly.
By the time Dad rescued you
from them, it was too late.
You'd-- Well...
[DARU]
Once I was able to locate you,
you were beyond help.
The ruthless torture
and endless experiments
had simply taken too much
of a toll on your mind.
When I said you were dead,
I meant it--you were.
Hold on, are you--
[DARU]
Mm.
The man I had known
for all those years
died that day.
Even if his body functioned,
his will to live was gone,
or so it seemed.
He was an empty shell,
though technically still alive.
--[gasps]
--[SUZUHA] I don't get it.
Why'd you say
he died, literally?
[DARU] I didn't have
a choice--I had to.
If they'd known,
they never would have
stopped chasing him,
or clamoring for control,
even in his
diminished condition.
That doesn't explain why you
wouldn't trust your own daughter
to keep it secret!
[OKABE] You're telling me
I've been lying there
in a comatose state
for 11 years?
[DARU] Yeah. Under the care
of a very select few
who knew the truth about you.
I resent that.
But more importantly,
why did he wake up
now after so long?
Because of the time
leap machine.
[DARU]
Exactly right.
Can you elaborate?
Someone got ahold
of my memories,
and they overwrote my brain
waves with memory data
from my 2011 self.
That's my theory.
And it's an astute
hypothesis, to boot.
We just salvaged that data
from an old PC.
Though, we didn't expect it
to work right away,
without further testing.
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
Deceiving the world
is one thing,
but then lying
to your own daughter?
Deceive the world?
That phrase is--
[DARU] I'm sure your mind
needs a while
to process
what's happened to you.
So, you should
take it easy for now.
I'll contact the others.
I'm sure they'll wanna
know you've woken up.
--Contact the others?
--[DARU] Yeah.
You've been out of commission
for 11 years.
The other lab members
have been waiting for this day,
and now it's arrived.
[FARIS]
No issues so far on my end.
All is well here, too.
This is the place, right?
You're 100% sure?
[FARIS]
Should be, meow.
And it's business as usual,
pick up the stuff and go.
[DARU]
Barrel Titor here.
Report in, comrades.
Cheshire Cat, reporting.
Something going on?
[DARU] Is Warrior there
with you, as well?
[FARIS]
Yes, meow.
Both of you, listen.
There's been a development.
[BOTH gasp]
Okarin has woken up, at last.
For real? Is that true?
[OKABE]
You're talking to--
Your old friends,
Ruka and Faris.
Just so you're aware,
they're the ones
who've been looking after
you all these years.
I owe my life to them.
[SUZUHA]
Hang on a minute.
Who gave those two
the order to go out
and pick up more rations
in the first place?
We didn't have anything planned
like that for them today.
Uh?
What? Are you sure
you've got the right info?
We got the message
late last night.
It said we had
to meet here today.
--It's a trap.
--[FARIS gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Ruka, Faris, get out of there!
[explosion]
--Let's go!
--Okey-dokey!
Hey, wait for me.
I'm coming, too.
[DARU]
No way.
You're in no shape for that.
I beg you!
Thank you, Suzuha.
This isn't good, meow.
We're all about
to get wiped out.
[RUKA]
I'll hold them off.
Run for it.
Everyone else go with Faris.
Come back here
with reinforcements.
Huh?
[FARIS]
That's insane. I won't do it!
There's no way
I'd just abandon you here.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
I refuse to die.
Not before I see Okabe.
Understood.
[yelling]
Let's move out!
What? Really?
[FARIS] Hang in there, Ruka.
We'll be back.
[glass shatters]
[SOLDIER C]
Huh?
[SOLDIER C grunting]
[DARU]
Suzuha! Twelve o'clock!
[MAN B]
Faris!
[FARIS]
Suzu-meow! Daru-meow!
[OKABE]
Faris!
[gasps]
[FARIS]
Kyouma...
[truck engine idling]
It's true?
Kyouma!
I can't believe it.
It is true. You're awake.
[OKABE]
I'm sorry that I worried you.
[SUZUHA]
Where's Ruka?
That's right!
We have to go back there
with reinforcements!
Ruka stayed behind
so that we could escape.
[BOTH gasp]
[tires screech]
Why don't I hear
any signs of combat?
[crumbling]
[footsteps]
[MAN B]
Over here! It's Ruka!
We're coming, hold on!
[FARIS]
Ruka-meow!
[OKABE breathing heavily]
[wind whistling]
[OKABE]
Rukako?
Is it you?
[OKABE]
Rukako!
Kyouma? Hey.
I'm here, Rukako!
[RUKA]
That name. I remember.
You're the only one who's ever
called me that, you know.
[coughing]
--[OKABE] Hang in there!
--Thank goodness.
Now that you've finally
come back to us,
I-- I can rest.
Because...
Don't talk.
[RUKA]
Listen, Kyouma.
I mastered it.
Can you believe that?
You tried to teach to me,
so many years ago.
The Seishin Zanma sword-fighting
style, do you remember?
I mastered it
and protected them.
Do you think
I could finally be
a true lab member?
I thought, since I did this,
maybe I'm worthy now.
I can be a proper comrade.
Yes.
Come on.
You always have been.
Don't you know?
From the beginning you were...
Lab member 0-0-6!
Thank you.
Ah...
I'm so happy.
This means that I can
face Mayuri and be proud.
[OKABE crying]
Please don't go!
[DARU]
That's a relief.
Ruka wanted to see you again,
more than anything in the world,
and was waiting so patiently
for the day when you'd wake up.
Now, in the end,
that wish
has finally been granted.
[gasping]
[OKABE sobbing]
[OKABE screams]
[door opens, closes]
[MAHO]
It feels like a million years.
Hi, Okabe.
[OKABE]
Hiyajo.
[MAHO]
It's not very strong.
We're always low
on everything, sorry.
It's fine.
I have to admit, I was
surprised to see you again.
Faris, too.
Yeah, of course, and I still
look like a little kid,
no matter how I old I get.
But when you're my age,
you can't help but count
that as a blessing.
I bet you think we're all
being cold about Ruka.
I mean, our close friend
just died,
and everyone around here's
so calm about it. Right?
Do you think we're heartless?
[OKABE]
No.
[MAHO] Ever since that day,
from July 7th of 2011,
until now,
so many people
have been killed.
Close family,
distant relatives,
most of our friends.
Adults and children alike.
We can't waste time mourning
every single person we've lost.
That's the reality
we live with now.
[OKABE]
I thought I understood.
Suzuha told me all about
it time and time again.
The future world
that my choice created.
All this misery is
a result of my weakness.
I got it, intellectually.
[crying]
[OKABE]
Not in my heart.
I understood as a scientist,
not as a human being!
I was denying the truth!
Trying to escape
the pain of reality,
like I could outrun it!
But even after I chose
to watch Kurisu die,
I still had to lose
Suzuha and Mayuri,
and Kagari,
and then Yuki.
Now Rukako.
After all this time
I still don't really understand
a damn thing, do I?
[DARU]
Eleven years ago.
I remember you saying
the same phrase.
So, I guess
you haven't changed.
[OKABE]
Daru.
You said you didn't understand
a damn thing then, either.
Right?
You told me something else, too.
That nothing is meaningless.
It may seem like it, but...
There are countless
failed futures,
and pasts we can never recover.
But even so,
beyond all of them,
there must be a path.
There has to be a way
to reach Steins Gate.
A way to reach it.
Steins Gate?
[OKABE]
Failed futures.
Pasts never to be recovered.
[OKABE]
All of them.
Every world line. I see.
[OKABE]
Hiyajo. Daru.
Right now I only have
my memories through 2011.
Because, using
the time leap machine,
you successfully overwrote
my memories from now
in the year 2036.
Do I understand correctly?
Yeah.
Somewhat reductive,
but you seem
to have the gist of it.
[OKABE]
Which means...
In this world, the time
leap machine still exists.
[BOTH gasp]
Get it ready for me.
Because I'm going to leap again.
Okarin?
But you can't!
[OKABE]
One more time.
I'm going back to find
the way to Steins Gate!