[SUZUHA gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Kagari? Wait!
--It's mine!
--[gasps]
[panting]
[whooshing]
Kagari.
[KAGARI] What have you done
with it? My precious gift.
The one Mommy gave me.
Your precious gift?
Huh.
--[door squeaks]
--[SUZUHA gasps]
[SUZUHA]
Oh, hey, Rumi.
[FARIS giggles]
[FARIS]
So, meow?
[SUZUHA] Well, I've only
got about a week left.
I feel a little guilty, though.
Suzu-meow, what is that?
[SUZUHA]
Ah. It's a photo.
Something I really treasure.
[FARIS]
Wow, is that you?
Which means the woman
next to you must be...
[SUZUHA]
Yup.
This is a picture of me
and my mom.
[FARIS]
Why do you look so grumpy?
Did you not want
to take the picture?
[SUZUHA]
To be honest, I don't remember.
It's true. I have no idea.
What else have I forgotten?
Suzu-meow.
[YUKI]
Hello!
[SUZUHA]
Uh. Mo-- I mean, Yuki!
It's been a while.
[SUZUHA]
My brother? Uh. He's, um,
I dunno, I guess
he's been doing well.
[YUKI]
Good. I'm glad to know that.
I haven't heard
from him in so long.
I thought he might have been
under the weather or something,
so I was getting
kind of worried.
But anyway, I'm glad to know
that everything's all right.
[grumbles]
[MAYURI]
I'm so excited to see Maho!
Keep your eyes
peeled for her.
She's pretty easy to miss.
Hey, Hiyajo!
[FARIS giggles]
Long time no see, friends.
What's up?
[MAYURI] Maho sure
seems to be doing well.
[OKABE]
Yeah.
Apparently she came to help
the Professor with his work.
She's quite a busy lady.
Poor Kagari.
I hope she's doing
all right, too.
Same here.
Daru and Suzuha
have been looking for her.
[MAYURI]
Mmm.
Oh, by the way,
where is Hashida?
He said he had
something important
to talk about with Suzu-meow,
so he wasn't able to come.
[MAHO]
Hmm.
What the hell, Dad?! For real?!
Whoa, what did I do to earn
that mean, stank face?
[SUZUHA]
Put your hand over your heart
and tell me
you don't really know.
My hand to my heart?
--Uhh...
--[SUZUHA growls]
Fine, then,
just keep on ghosting her!
Someone's gonna come along
and pay her more attention,
you'll see!
Huh? Say that again?
What do you mean?
I've seen it for myself.
The other day Mom
was talking to some guy
and acting all friendly
and flirty with him.
She was flirting?
When's the last time
you even saw her?
It was... the day
I went to visit Fubuki.
But not since then?
[DARU]
Mm-mm.
[SUZUHA growls]
So why haven't you
reached out to her?
[DARU]
Well, uh, because,
I've been super busy working
on the Time Leap Machine,
and all kinds
of other important stuff.
[SUZUHA] You would make time
if you really wanted to!
[gasps] You're right.
Well, what if you don't
ask her out in time
and she just ends up
marrying someone else?
[DARU]
Mmm.
--Maybe this is no big deal.
--[SUZUHA gasps]
How do you know
it wasn't some guy
asking her for directions
or trying to sell her
something.
You don't know
she was flirting.
[SUZUHA]
Yeah, and what if you're wrong?
If you're so worried about it,
why are you talkin' to me?
Shouldn't you be
talking to her?
Why aren't you even remotely
concerned about this?
Can't you muster
a shred of sympathy
for the fact that
my entire existence
might be at stake here?
Come on, I'm talking
to you right now,
so doesn't that tell us
that you will be born
at the same time in the future?
Huh? Wait, is that...?
Miss Amane in the future?
Ooh! Loli Suzuha is lovely!
You're missing the point,
Dad! Look closer!
[DARU]
Hmm?
Why is your lower half so faded?
It's been doing that
for a while now.
Huh--? That's just like
Back to the Future.
[SUZUHA]
Dad!
What?
[SUZUHA]
You have zero confidence, Dad.
[sighs]
And because you don't
believe in yourself,
you're avoiding
making the first move.
You're just sitting on your ass,
hoping that Mom
will do it for you.
Is that right?
You're not wrong.
The future doesn't wait for
those who refuse to take action.
That's something
you said to me
when I was a little girl.
Whoa, I really said all that?
But that's not what--
Listen to me!
If you and Mom
aren't moving forward,
I might be in real jeopardy,
do you understand?
This is serious!
[gasps]
[MAYURI]
Too-too-roo!
We're here! Hi! Huh?
Ruka, Moeka, I wasn't
expecting you guys.
What's happening?
Hey, Mayuri.
[SUZUHA] Perfect timing.
We need your help here.
[gasps]
[MAYURI]
Okay, I see now.
Before his date
with Yuki tomorrow,
we need to teach Daru
to have confidence in himself.
Is that what's going on?
[SUZUHA]
Mm-hmm.
I'm clueless about
this sort of thing,
which is why I asked
all of you to help me out.
I'm guessing the doctored
photo worked, then?
[SUZUHA]
Brother!
Yes?
Our mission
commences immediately!
Operation objective:
upon conclusion of his date
with Amane Yuki tomorrow,
Hashida Daru will face
and confess
his feelings for her.
[gasping]
Tell Miss Amane that?
You've gone crazy!
That is the wrong attitude,
mister! Try again!
Miss Suzuha!
Yes! I will, Miss Suzuha!
[ALEXIS laughs]
The poor girl was
so desperate to see you
that she practically begged me
to let her come to Japan.
It was just adorable.
[MAHO] I did no such thing,
and you know it!
[OKABE chuckles]
[ALEXIS]
By the way, Rintaro.
regarding that report
you and I discussed
the other day,
--are you making any progress?
--[phone vibrates]
Oh. I actually
brought it with me.
[ALEXIS]
Wow! Color me impressed!
[MAHO gasps]
Suzuha?
[OKABE]
It's nothing remarkable,
but it's complete.
[ALEXIS]
Rintaro.
Modesty isn't
always a good policy
in the real world,
you know. Hmph.
Particularly if you're hoping
to compete in America.
Apologies.
I mean, thank you, Professor.
I'll make sure to set
aside ample time tonight
to give this report of yours
my undivided attention.
If it's good enough,
then you might even
be able to transfer
sooner than
we previously thought.
Great!
And I'm sure
Maho would love that!
Professor!
--[ALEXIS, OKABE chuckling]
--[phone vibrating]
[OKABE]
What's up?
[MAYURI]
Ah, Okarin?
Um, listen. A bunch of us
are hanging out at
the lab right now.
So, I was wondering
if you wanted to join us, maybe?
At the lab?
[MAYURI]
Yeah. Will you come?
Uh...
I'm sorry.
I can't. Next time.
Oh, all right.
Well, it's no big deal.
Miss ya.
Keep working hard, Okarin!
[DARU groaning]
[FARIS] If you wanna steal
a lady's heart,
you've gotta know
where all the hippest,
tastiest restaurants
in town are, meow!
So, without further ado,
we're gonna be uploading data
about the best eateries
and the appropriate manners
into your head, 'kay?
Miss Faris, ma'am!
Yes, Miss Faris, ma'am!
We know that Yuki
is really into cosplay,
and that's something.
Along those lines, I think
if you wear a different outfit
than your usual get-up,
it might set her heart
all aflutter,
you know what I mean?
Miss Mayuri!
--Yes! Thanks, Miss Mayuri!
--[MAYURI giggles]
I think... the most
important thing
is that you really understand
how a woman's heart works.
[phone clicking]
[exhales]
Well, brother,
whaddaya think?
You feelin' confident yet?
Huh? Uh, yeah, sure.
[GIRLS groan]
[door closes]
I can't believe
you guys made me
come over just for this.
It's a bad joke, right?
[MAYURI]
Hey, Maho! Where's Okarin?
The professor told me
to leave without him.
Does this mean
you're gonna help us?
[MAHO]
Of course.
I sure as hell don't want
Hashida to stay like this.
Now fill me in
on the details, ladies.
[SUZUHA]
Better sit down.
[MAHO]
So, in other words,
we're trying to boost
Hashida's confidence with women.
[SUZUHA]
What is that?
[MAHO]
For now, let's just call it
an experimental
training system
with a couple
of customizations.
Essentially, it's something
of a rudimentary
sleep-learning device.
[SUZUHA]
Huh?
Hashida Daru.
Whether you realize it or not,
you are a ladies' man.
[gasps]
Not even Don Giovanni
could compete
with your raw charisma
and sensual energy.
[DARU]
I... I'm a sensual ladies' man.
[MAHO]
Now, open your eyes.
[chuckles]
--[DARU] Yuki.
--Huh?
[chuckles]
Oh, uh, Hashida?
[DARU]
The usual, my good man.
Yes, Mister Hashida.
Wow, you must
come here a lot.
[chuckles]
Because I'm such
a successful man.
Oh. I see.
So, how did I do
over there, ma'am?
You were perfect, meow!
I don't know.
How do you think
things are going?
It has to be going well.
He's got this!
Maho-meow's idea sure
is paying in dividends, huh?
Well, to be honest,
I had no idea
it would be this effective.
[inaudible]
[YUKI]
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
I agree, and yet...
...can't hold a candle to you.
Uh...
That's sweet of you to say.
[MAYURI]
This is so romantic!
[SUZUHA]
All that's left is for him
to deliver the final blow!
--Come on!
--[FARIS] Look, meow!
--Listen, today was--
--Yuki.
Hold on. Hashida, I...
Just let me say. Yuki...
Say what?
Yuki, will you...
[gasps]
Will you...
[DARU]
I really blew it.
No, Dad.
Get ahold of yourself.
It isn't like she flat-out
rejected you, you know?
[DARU]
You're totally wrong, noob.
No matter how you slice it,
she hates me!
[DARU]
Will you...
[YUKI]
Oh, no. Look how late it is!
[gasps]
I should really get going now.
[YUKI] I had a lot of fun
with you today.
Thanks again for everything.
[footsteps]
[GIRLS groan]
[DARU]
I knew it was all pointless.
A girl like her would never
want to be with a guy like me,
not in the real world, anyway.
But I acted all cocky
and misread her signals
like an idiot.
To think I had the nerve
to hold her hand!
I mean, just look at me!
I'm gross and sweaty
and stupid.
My hands are
all sticky and nasty.
I bet the whole time
we were together
she was thinking, "Ew, you're
disgusting. Let go of my hand
and don't ever touch me again,
you greasy pervert!"
[SUZUHA]
Stop it, Dad.
You know Mom's not like that!
[DARU]
This was all a lame pipe dream
from the beginning.
[SUZUHA gasps]
[DARU]
I mean, think about it.
Why would a beautiful
girl like her
ever willingly
decide to marry
a worthless piece
of crap like me?
That just doesn't happen,
not outside of dating SIMs.
Miss Amane will end up
with somebody else.
[SUZUHA] Please don't
say stuff like that to me, Dad!
[DARU]
But you said it yourself,
it's already starting to happen.
Look, Dad. It's fine.
I'm sorry, but I just need
some time alone, okay?
[door closes]
Oh, Suzuha. I'm so sorry.
[SUZUHA]
Thanks, Mayuri.
No. This whole thing
is my fault,
'cause I'm the one
who doctored that photo.
Yeah, and I took it too far.
No, stop.
It's not your fault.
[crowd chattering]
[SUZUHA]
I'm to blame for this.
Again. Just like before.
[SUZUHA]
Hey, Mom!
Mom, wait! [giggles]
[laughing]
[YUKI]
Suzuha!
--Watch out!
--[gasps]
[gunfire]
[gasping]
[rapid gunfire]
[screams]
[SUZUHA]
Um, Dad?
Do you think we could talk?
[DARU]
Sure.
[SUZUHA] I've told you
about the time I come from.
It's a chaotic,
terrifying place.
I never had a chance to spend
much time with you and Mom.
We didn't have that luxury.
[SUZUHA]
Now I do.
[screaming]
[sobbing, gasping]
And the truth is,
I just wanted to experience it.
To see my mom and dad,
who created
and gave birth to me,
to watch them
spending time together.
I thought if I could,
then everything would be okay.
I'd be heading down
the right path.
I felt like it would be
the proof that I needed.
I'm sorry,
but the story about
her flirting with another guy,
and me fading
from the picture?
It was all just a lie.
I made everything up.
[DARU] Well, I kinda figured
that was the case.
[SUZUHA gasps]
--[DARU] I knew the whole time.
--[SUZUHA] You did?
[DARU] But it doesn't matter
whether you lied,
or if the whole thing was true.
Honestly?
I just wanted someone
to give me an extra shove
in that direction.
I've been acting
totally selfish.
I'm the one
who needs to apologize.
No, Dad...
Hi, Miss Amane?
I'm sorry about today.
Sure. So, uh, listen.
[inhales]
Would you be willing to meet up
with me again sometime tomorrow?
--Yeah.
--[SUZUHA gasps]
[DARU]
Of course.
Sounds great.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[SUZUHA]
He did it.
Oh, Dad.
You're really incredible.
[MAHO sighs]
All right.
How the heck am I supposed
to do this on my own?
[DARU]
Miss Amane!
[chuckles]
[giggles]
[inaudible]
[YUKI] I had an amazing time
with you today.
Thank you again for all of it.
[DARU]
Right back atcha.
Thanks for hanging out with me,
and two days in a row!
[BOTH chuckle]
[laughs]
Uh, Miss Amane?
Personally, I like you better
when you're being yourself.
You're more fun this way.
[giggles]
[stammers]
Well...
Uh. Thank you, I--
C'mon.
I, uh-- When I--
Whenever I think about you,
I feel so Moe Moe Kyun!
Great.
[SUZUHA chuckles]
[gasps]
[SUZUHA laughs]
[laughing continues]
[SUZUHA]
Thank goodness.
I can do this now.
[gasps]
[phone vibrates]
[MAYURI]
Think we could meet today?
There's so much I want
to talk to you about.
[laughs]
[ALEXIS]
Rintaro.
Thanks for waiting.
[OKABE]
Oh, sure. I don't mind, sir.
So sorry I'm late.
My work at the hospital
just seems to be
one problem after another.
But I did have a chance
to read your report.
There are a few sections
that need a little
polishing up,
but overall, your ideas
and viewpoints
are quite intriguing.
Do you have
some time right now?
I'd like to go
over it with you
and ask a few questions.
[OKABE]
Of course.
I'd be honored, Professor.
[YUKI]
Your brother really cares
about you a lot, Suzuha.
Yeah. I'm lucky.
My family's pretty amazing.
[YUKI giggles]
So, um, my brother.
I only ask that you take
good care of him for me.
I promise.
I'll do that.
He makes me feel Moe Moe Kyun!
[gasps]
[YUKI]
Suzuha.
I'm so glad
I got to be your mom!
Thank you, sweetheart.
What? This is so weird.
I'm crying, but why?
It's okay.
You don't have
to say anything.
[SUZUHA cries]
[crying continues]
[SUZUHA]
Don't you wanna be in it, too?
[DARU]
No, no, it's fine!
Yuki and I will have
tons of opportunities
to take pics together.
Okay, smile, girls!
--[camera clicks]
--[YUKI giggles]
[YUKI] You sure you don't
want to come?
Yeah, If I stick around
any longer bugging you two,
I'll really start to feel
like a third wheel.
Well, shall we?
Yeah.
[SUZUHA]
Thank you so much...
Mom.
[wind whistling]