[SOMA] (Gagging)
Disgusting!
These were never meant
to go together...
I'm like a genius!
Squid tentacles
and peanut butter...
(Evil laugh)
This is so nasty!
(Continued laugh)
[JOICHIRO]
Soma!
Your friend's here.
'Kay!
(Swishing)
Well, let's do this!
(Roaring flame)
(Sizzling)
(Pans rattling)
(Oohs and ahhs)
Please enjoy.
Whoo. Bon appetite, my lady!
Thank you very much!
Dude...
Those two are battling
it out again!
Oh! Look. Mayu's the
judge this time.
(Orgasmic squeals and whimpers)
Ahh...
(Soft exhale)
(Crowd whispering)
Here we go...
You think today's
the day?
Shh! Mayu's trying
to think, okay?
Hm.
This one here.
(Crowd applauds)
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Well there it is!
Daddy Yukihira wins again!
(Soma gasps)
Ah!
(Growl)
[JOICHIRO]
Soma...
Looks like you still have some
learnin' to do, don'tcha?
Well, I guess I'll
take the loss today...
Y'know to say
something like that,
you have to beat me
at least ONCE!
You're sittin' at almost 500
losses, that about right?
Huh?!
Don't even, that's only 489!
(Restaurant chatter)
[JOICHIRO]
Well don't worry, you'll be
there before you know it.
[SOMA]
Whatever, Dad!
You don't know!
Ahhh...
Mmm.
Gah!
Ah!
Ohhh!
The old man's fried rice
is freakin' ridiculous!
I, like, can't believe I can
totally get something like this
right in our neighborhood!
I'm losing my
freakin' mind!
But still! Um, Soma,
yours was really tasty, too!
(Solemn bell toll)
I'd just never had fried rice
anything like this before!
Yeah... Thanks...
Uh?
Would you care to try
a brand new dish
I created earlier today?
I think you'll
really like it.
Huh? Are you sure?
I would love to try it!
(Oozing)
[SOMA]
It's fried peanut‐butter
squid tentacles.
Huh?
Mayu!
He's not doing
this again!
He may be taking it
too far this time!
Why don't you take
a little bite?
(Cowering)
It's so putrid,
you're gonna freak.
No...
(Cackle)
Ah! Mmmf.
(Mayu screams)
Ah!
(Screams and moans)
NO! PLEASE!
(Screams)
[MAYU]
"The squid and the
peanut butter combination
is so offensive
in so many ways, it's as if my
entire body is being violated."
[NARRATOR]
The young lady gave a
very... detailed account.
[NARRATOR]
The art of cooking is indeed a
vast and stupefying spectrum...
A wasteland dotted with endless
examples
of the "delectable"
and the "repulsive."
And that is where
I want to be.
Walking the reaches
of the food universe.
Walk it on your own,
you stupid nitwit!
(Whimpering)
You just hang in there, Mayu,
you're going to be okay.
Peanut butter squid...
the absolute horror!
He takes strange pride in people
eating even his worst dishes.
If it weren't for him
pulling crap like that,
he would be a pretty
awesome chef...
Nice try, but
I've made worse.
Remember that dried sardine
concoction with the pureed
strawberry jam?
How could I forget?
[SOMA] That one should
have been banned.
I know, right?
But my peanut butter squid
is way more gross!
Please! Sardines‐and‐jam!
[SOMA]
Peanut butter squid
is so much worse!
[PATRONS]
Yep. He is definitely
his father's son.
[JOICHIRO] Not as bad as mine.
[SOMA] Mine was worse!
(Opening Song)
(Dog barking)
(Motorcycle drives by)
(Street chatter)
[SOMA]
Okay, here's your
liver and onions!
Can I get a meat‐and‐tofu
plate, please?
Say, uh... And I'd like
to have the daily special.
Right, you got it!
One meat‐and‐tofu! One daily!
Comin' right up.
[MAN 1] Man, I'm stuffed!
[MAN 2] That was incredible!
[MAN 3] Really great, guys.
[JOICHIRO] Thanks alot!
[SOMA]
See ya next time!
(Water running)
(Dishes clattering)
[JOICHIRO]
Soma.
When you're done
with that,
could you put out
the charcoal?
Huh?
I could've done
better today.
I should've given that
rice another three flips.
[SOMA]
Well, the year will be
over soon and I'll be
able to devote more time
to perfecting my techniques.
I gotta pass up the old man
as soon as possible.
Then, I will be the one
carrying the restaurant!
(Door slides open)
(Numerous footsteps)
Oh! Wel‐
(Angry growl)
[WOMAN]
Pardon us for
the intrusion.
It would appear you're preparing
to close for the night.
(Door slides closed)
I hope you don't mind
the late hour.
My apologies.
Hello, good to see you again...
You remember me?
Can I get you something?
Today's specials are
the Kinmedai sashimi
plate and then a...
Oh, no thanks, the reason
I'm here today...
...is to further explain the
plan that we discussed.
I would be happy to go over
it again with you if you like.
[WOMAN]
We would love to follow
the Garden Residence concept
and bring to the area a
"comfortable and luxurious"
high‐rise to this‐ Oh!
[SOMA]
Yeah... I know.
You want to drive us
out of here, correct?
Trust me. I've heard
it all before, lady.
Go on home. We have no
intention of closing up shop.
So you've said.
I'll leave you my card.
In case you
change your mind.
[YAEKO]
I know things
aren't easy.
I mean small businesses
are having it harder
and harder these days.
It's pretty rough
out there.
[YAEKO]
I've heard a lot of folks
are having trouble
just getting by each day.
Yeah, well, that's not
the case with this place.
Oh, is that so?
[SOMA]
Here at Yukihira,
we do whatever it takes
to give the customer
what they want.
It sounds like you are just
the picture‐perfect little
restaurant, aren't you?
(Light giggle)
However, what if you
COULDN'T give your customers
what they want?
How exactly would you handle
a situation like that?
(Inhale)
[SOMA]
If that were to happen...
We would gracefully
shut our doors...
and go out of business
for all eternity.
(Crackling)
Can I take your
word on that?
Yep.
Very well.
I'll be back.
(Door slides open)
(Slow footsteps)
[SOMA]
Dad! Scatter some salt!
Unsully this place!
[JOICHIRO]
Nah. That'd be a waste.
Don't worry about it.
(Campus chatter)
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Hey, what are
you doing later?
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Wanna do some karaoke?
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Yeah. What're
you gonna sing?
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Anime songs, duh.
[AKI]
Mayu! C'mon!
Oh!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Don't you know anything else.
Like, some glam rock, maybe?
(Crows cawing)
(Phone vibrating)
Hm?
Hey, Dad. What's up?
[JOICHIRO]
You back already?
No, I was buying some
stuff for breakfast. Why?
[JOICHIRO]
I need to go on a
little errand today.
Huh? Oh yeah?
I won't be back till
tomorrow, so don't bother
opening up the shop.
Okay...
Son...
Huh?
What are your plans after
this school year?
Uh...
What else? Practice cooking
with you at the shop.
I see.
(Phone hangs up)
[SOMA]
That was weird.
Wait a minute...
What "errand" could make
my dad close the shop?
I can't imagine
what it would be.
I guess when it
comes down to it,
I don't really know all
that much about my Dad's
life outside the kitchen.
Or his past for that matter.
Ah!
[SOMA]
The meat!
It's all ruined!
And everything in
the fridge...
Did we get robbed?
No, it doesn't look like it.
AH!
(Splat)
(Gasp)
[YAEKO]
Oh, you poor thing.
But you know, it does
look much nicer out here
than it did yesterday.
Perhaps it's because
that eyesore of a sign
has been covered up.
Ah, I'm in the mood to indulge
in a big thick juicy steak...
I always like to have one
while in Roppongi.
Something nice and marbled,
of course.
Where the natural flavors merge
together in luscious harmony.
(Sizzling)
There's really nothing
in the world quite like it.
[YAEKO]
So, little man...
I'd like to place an order.
I would like for you to give me
a thick and juicy cut of meat.
What? Don't tell me
you can't make it for me.
But I'm a paying customer.
[YAEKO]
I think I remember you
saying something yesterday.
Hmm. What was it? Oh...
That if you can't provide
what the customer needs,
then you would
close your doors.
Oh! Perhaps your signage
is just right.
Looks like you've
already started.
I suppose you'll be
clearing everything out
of the dining area next.
(Cackle)
(Exhale)
[SOMA]
You want a juicy meat dish...?
Uh?
[SOMA]
Will that complete your
order for today, ma'am?
(Swishing)
Well just sit tight, and I'll
have it right out for you.
And then you will never come in
this restaurant ever again!
Ah!
(All stammering)
(Monster growl)
Order up!
Heh.
(Chopping and dicing)
(Roaring)
(Escaping steam)
(Sizzling)
(Dishes clatter)
(Strong impact)
(Men gasp)
Wait a second...
You did take everything
out of the fridge, right?
Uh‐huh! We ruined every single
last piece of meat in there.
I‐I distinctly requested a
thick and juicy meat dish!
What exactly is this kid going
to make without any fresh meat?
(Fwip fwip)
(Sizzling)
(Gasp)
How could he...
...possibly make...
...such a wonderful...
[YAEKO]
...pork roast?!
Well I can tell ya...
this here is actually a potato.
I wrapped it with some
thick‐cut bacon I had for
tomorrow's breakfast.
It's what I call a
"pseudo pork roast"!
(Gasp)
Did he say a potato?
A "Pseudo"...
..."pork roast"?
Yep. That's right.
First, I steamed
the potatoes, and‐
[YAEKO]
Whatever, kid...
Uh. What's up? Is
there a problem here?
Are you trying to
pull one over on me?
Uhh!
I told you to make
me a MEAT dish!
There's no room for
negotiation on this!
If you can't provide,
you close your shop!
Look here! All my head chefs
are highly respected
and make their livings
at top‐notch restaurants
and first‐rate hotels
that I'VE put together!
This place is a dump!
[YAEKO]
And from where I'm sitting...
There's no value in
this failure existing!
Oh!
If you want to see the
"value" in Yukihira...
Then you will quickly
learn it from this dish.
Please, eat up!
(Heavy breath)
(Gasp)
Ooh!
Aaah...
(Stunned)
(Steam hisses)
(Quick inhale)
Ahh...
Om...
(Sensuous moaning)
Each time I bite down...
the savory juices
from the slow‐cooked bacon...
overflow to every corner
of my mouth!
(Whimpers and squeals)
It looks like somebody's
enjoying their meal.
(Gasp)
[SOMA]
From the very restaurant
you were just insulting.
(Yaeko gasps)
Shall I tell you...?
The secret to
its flavor.
[SOMA]
Once the potatoes
are nice and soft...
I grabbed some fibrous mushrooms
to soak up the fat.
Then, I diced up some onion
to bump up the sweetness, and
then kneaded both of them in.
Next, I wrapped it with
the thick‐cut bacon.
Then I slowly cooked
it in the oven.
That made the bacon
nice and crispy.
That's when the potato
and mushrooms did their thing,
and soaked up all
the tasty bacony goodness.
Which in turn...
created the beautiful
combination of
crispy‐on‐the‐outside
and juicy in the middle.
Almost "sensual,"
don'tcha think?
(All groaning)
[SOMA]
Awhile back, when I was making a
potato salad for a customer...
I messed up the plating,
and the juices from the
protein accidently seeped
into the potato salad.
That's where I got the
inspiration for this dish...
It came from my "failure."
(Gasp) Uh, well...
It's not as if... this thing...
can be called a meat dish!
(Struggling)
But... I can't...
I can't stop!
Ah. Ahh!
(Hard exhale)
I wan't more!
It's so... so succulent!
Ah!
Uh, what?
What are you doing?
If you want to have more,
you'll have to make me
a promise.
(Sizzling)
That you won't come after
this restaurant again.
Hah! I don't think so, kid!
Okeedokee...
[SOMA]
I guess this wasn't
good enough then.
Oh well...
(Flunkies gasp)
[SOMA]
I'll just have
to throw it out!
[YAEKO]
No! Wait!
I promise! I promise! I promise!
Oh yeah?
(Fluttered breaths)
I want more... I do.
I. Beg. You. Please.
Heh!
(Torrential steam)
(Bad guys gasp)
[FLUNKY]
Whoa...
(Moan)
(Screaming)
(Light moans)
Wooaahhh!
[ALL]
Om.
Mm!
(Foodgasmic moans)
OH, YES!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
(Screaming)
[ALL]
Meat juices!
(Swish)
(Moan)
You're welcome!
(Birds chirping)
[SOMA]
I am not letting this place
close, no matter what!
Yukihira is the "temple" where
I will master my cooking.
(Meow)
(Footsteps)
Huh?
[SOMA]
Hey, Pops!
What in the world
happened here?
It wasn't really
that big a deal.
We just had a few customers
who were being kinda rude.
Soma...
Huh?
For a couple of years,
I'm afraid...
...we'll have to
shut down the shop.
AAHH!
(Loud bang)
But we'll be
back up soon.
I'll have to apologize
to our regulars.
Apologize to your SON!
An old colleague of
mine has contacted me
about wanting to
work together again.
Hmph! What?!
[JOICHIRO]
I'm going to be
very busy for awhile,
so I won't be available.
[SOMA]
This is bullcrap.
Dad! We need to talk!
[JOICHIRO]
I'm leaving as soon
as I finish packing.
[SOMA]
Wait.
I'll wire you some money for
expenses every now and then.
I said wait!
Tch. I...
I don't...
wanna lose this place!
It's time for you to
go, too, Soma.
Come back once you've
learned what you're made of.
(Grunt)
Cooking school?
Why would I need to go to
someplace like that?
[JOICHIRO]
The timing's right.
The shop will be closed,
and it'll give you a chance
to earn credits
for high school.
[JOICHIRO]
It'll be some good
practice for you.
Good grief...
This is dumb.
Paying some yahoo to teach me
to cook is just stupid.
I don't need a bunch of
has‐beens blathering
about nothin'!
Ahhh...
Today, we will go over a
dish that is simple to make
and easy to digest.
Thank you
for your wisdom!
(Distant shriek)
I am an
absolute failure!
[BLONDE SCHOOLBOY]
That's it!
My life is over!
[FATHER]
Please! I'll pay you!
10 million, no,
no, 20 million!
Just, please,
don't expel my son!
(Sobbing)
[SOMA]
What the...?
Geh!
[JOICHIRO]
Know this, son...
This is one of the
best culinary schools
in the country.
It's a super‐elite institution
with a graduation
rate of less than 10%.
(Speechless gasp)
(Ending Song)
(Clang)
PFFFFT!
(Distorted music)
VILE!
Gah!
Waagh!
That broth is horrendous!
It, like, tricks you
into thinking you're
enjoying yourself
and then a jukebox
drops on your face!
Did she say jukebox?
That was
kinda random...
(Grunt)
(Students cower)
Please, please, forgive
my embarrassing oversight,
Miss Erina!
Honestly!
I am not amused.
Not amused one bit.
[NARRATOR]
Next time...
on the second course
of Food Wars:
"God Tongue"
Bon appétit.
[MAYU]
Uh, peanut butter squid...