[JOICHIRO]
Sorry to throw you right
into this without warning,
but I wanna see
how far you've come along.
Or how far you may
have fallen behind.
Show me, right here and now.
I'd say it's been too long
since we've had a proper food
battle...
Now show me.
I knew you'd come
back eventually.
Well I'm glad to
know this is why.
Well I'm glad you're glad.
We gonna do this or not?
I'm ready when you are, old man!
[ISSHIKI] I never dreamed that
Soma would be the son of a
former member of The Ten.
[JOICHIRO](Laughs)
Yeah, I can see where you
wouldn't expect that.
He lacks some refinement.
The only skills he's
picked up so far have
been at a Japanese eatery.
Doesn't exactly call to mind
the prestige of this academy,
does it?
[ISSHIKI]
Haha! Yes, true enough.
That's how it seems,
but ever since Soma
and I first battled,
I feel very confident that
he'll be making some big waves
at this school.
Oh really?
All right, as the theme for
this culinary battle...
Hey, gonna need
a judge in here!
Guh!
So! What're you
in the mood to eat?
Who's the judge?
Hehehe. So the love of
battles runs in the family.
You two are cut
from the same cloth.
I swear...
Miss Fumio!
Joichiro asked me
last night to judge.
I'll be running this challenge
whether you like it or not!
This certainly is
worth watching, isn't it?
Gah! You scared
me to death!
What are you doing here,
you strange little boy?!
Well, Miss Fumio,
I was coming back from
working out in the fields,
when I caught wind
of a rather interesting
challenge...
Well, unfortunately, you can
only watch the battle.
It would take an odd number
of judges for us‐
Ooh?
Um, Megumi?
Huh?
Oh, hey, Soma.
Good morning.
Uh! Oh man, Megumi...
You've got some major
bags under your eyes.
Huh. I'm really tired,
but whenever I think
about that training camp,
I can't seem to make
myself go back to sleep...
We really need to hurry up and
catch something so we can start
cooking!
Uwahaha!
Ah!
Ahhh!
Hey, look out!
What should I do?
I'm sorry!
(Sobbing)
You know... I'm surprised
I even made it out alive.
You're safe now, Megumi.
I think you should
just get some rest.
Ah, her timing's just right.
Come here, Megumi.
Huh?
Great, that will give us
our three judges.
Are we all agreed?
Mm‐hmm.
Yeah.
Let's see, I'm getting
pretty up there in age.
My stomach can't
handle anything
too rich in the morning.
And I've got students
up at all hours...
That's it!
The challenge is...
Make a dish that makes someone
feel young and invigorated,
especially first thing
in the morning.
You're free to use whatever
you like, provided it's
available in the kitchen.
Your time limit is one hour.
And so...
BEGIN!
Something light and easy to
eat...
Let's see here...
And it has to be
nutritious, as well.
Got it!
Huh? Um, what?!
Why are they battling
each other?
Megumi, glad
you joined us.
I see you're
finally awake.
Huh? Yeah! But what's
this all about?!
Soma, you're father's a
former member of The Ten.
There's no way
you can win!
Yeah, well, at "Yukihira,"
we battled each other
all the time.
Our first challenge was...
my last year of
elementary school.
I can't even imagine.
You battled an adult?
That seems like something
you'd do...
Hey, wait! Did
you actually win?!
Well, let me think
about it...
Don't even. You know
where you stand.
You're at 500 losses
right now, aren'tcha?
It is 489, old man!
Got a great memory
for such a loser.
Huh...?
A food battle? Really?
Yeah. And I'd like you
to be the judge.
Well, it's been a while
since I've watched you
in a food challenge.
I'd be happy to judge your
little family skirmish.
But you have to promise me
you won't go soft on him
and pull your punches just
because he's your son.
You don't need to
worry about that.
Never gone easy on him
in a battle before...
And I don't plan
on it today, either.
[MEGUMI]
Huh? An apple?
That may be his father,
but he's the former No. 2 seat
on The Ten.
To challenge him like this...
What is he thinking?
I see...
So these are his roots.
No matter how great the
obstacles Soma has had to face,
he never backs down
from a challenge.
This must be the source.
Though far behind his father
in terms of skill,
he has kept taking him on...
Unaffected by the
489 straight losses.
So who do think will
be finishing up first?
Sorry for the wait!
Look at that.
[SOMA]
An apple risotto.
Now... Time to eat.
[FUMIO]
Risotto, you say?
[MEGUMI]
Ohmigosh!
It really has finely cut
cubes of apple in there.
Hmm... Adding fruit
to risotto...
That's a nice twist all right.
It has a fresh
sweet‐and‐sour scent to it.
Is that lemon I
detect in there too?
That's right.
Smells wonderfully refreshing.
Judging from the scent,
this would rouse a sluggish
stomach and get the appetite
going.
It could even
wake a person up.
An apple risotto!
Well then...
What counts is how it tastes.
Mmmm...
The apple has a crunchy texture
and a slight sweetness...
And the onion is simmered
till it's nice and soft.
The bacon,
fried nice and crisp,
accents the risotto's overall
mild apple flavor.
(Foodgasmic moan)
To a slumbering soul...
It's like a gentle
awakening to the world.
Ah. Ah!
A sweet, compassionate kiss...
from the bright and
crispy Prince Apple!
Apple!
So good!
Feel free to season it
with black pepper.
It'll change the flavor,
but it still works!
Let's see...
[FUMIO]
The piping‐hot sweetness of
the apple and the onions...
[ISSHIKI]
The savory intensity
of the black pepper!
The black pepper, sprinkled
on top this white dish...
It creates a contrast
between sight and taste!
[BOTH]
It's like a waltz
between black and white!
I'm swooning!
It's as if it's seeping into
every pore of my tired body.
I see, it has vitamins
and lipids, as well as
carbohydrates.
The rice is cooked up nice and
fluffy, so it's easy to digest
through this old stomach.
[FUMIO]
It's the perfect dish for
someone just out of bed!
But still, how did he
even get it like this?
What do you mean, Isshiki?
The apple flavor
is so prominent,
even with the rice and onions.
If he'd simmered it long enough
to achieve such a blend,
the apple should've
gotten all mushy.
So how is it still so crunchy?
You're right.
But how did he do it?
Because of this...
My secret ingredient!
You used apple juice?
[SOMA]
As I was simmering the onions
and cooked the rice,
I added the juice
a little at a time.
Then added in the sliced apple
after that, and cooked it all
at a low temperature.
That's how it retained its
texture.
Yes... What a remarkable idea!
He used the juice to give
this dish its overall
essence of "apple."
What a marvel he is!
To think, he could
rise to the theme
of this challenge
with such precision
and knowledge...
Just how many tricks does
this boy have up his sleeve?
[FUMIO]
An apple risotto was
the perfect answer for
a tired old woman like me!
I can't imagine anything
that could top it.
He is such a fearsome man.
[FUMIO]
You can feel it...
Soma Yukihira's dish could be
called a perfect 100,
yet Joichiro seems
like he'll easily beat it.
Sorry for the wait.
[JOICHIRO]
Go ahead...
Dig in, guys...
Appalling.
It tastes like
50,000 blue crabs
have trampled over an
idyllic countryside.
I'm not amused at all!
Everything he made for us last
night was cooked to perfection.
And now that he's doing
a battle, just what
kind of dish will he make?
It's a true honor to be able
to witness the cooking of
a great member of The Ten!
Heh! Even as a student, Joichiro
was renowned for his aggressive
and creative cooking style.
Watch closely now!
Please enjoy the meal.
It's a Joichiro‐style ramen
in a thick broth.
Huh?!
What?!
[ALL]
Ramen?!
[MEGUMI]
I‐in the morning?
Ah! That broth looks so rich...
True, ramen is eaten for
breakfast in some regions,
but this looks like a thick,
dense seafood broth.
[ISSHIKI]
For sleep‐deprived
Megumi and our somewhat
aged Fumio,
this dish is a little much.
Joichiro, creativity
has its limits!
I swear, you were like
this back then, too!
Even in a Food War,
you had no problem
serving a new dish you'd
just concocted or some
other strange creation!
That's why your opponents
were always able to beat
you left and right
during all your
Food War challenges!
Hmph! I was a little rough
around the edges back then, huh?
And nothing seems
to have changed!
Huh?
Ms. Fumio, this broth
looks really rich,
but it actually has a pleasant
and mellow scent coming from it.
Uh! True enough...
Well, let's judge this thing.
I... I love this!
The noodles are
infused with citrus.
It's so rich and enticing
I find myself wanting more.
[ISSHIKI]
One thing's for sure...
I...
Just...
Can't...
Stop...
[BOTH]
eating... THIS!
The broth is a delicate blend
of soymilk and charred miso.
But how on Earth does it retain
its rich flavorful taste?
You'd be surprised.
I added a grated ebi‐imo root
which contains a robust flavor.
That made the broth both
creamy and rich.
Ah!
Feels like my body just keeps
getting warmer and warmer.
I feel it.
It's from the hot sesame oil,
grated fresh ginger,
and minced scented garlic.
The soy milk mellows them out,
so they slowly caress
the body from the inside.
And these toppings are
an incredible parade of detail
to adorn the finished dish.
Thinly sliced lotus and burdock
roots fried to a nice crisp,
with carrots and turnips
grilled over coals giving it
just a hint of char.
Then, sprinkled with rock salt
to draw out their sweetness.
Just like garnishes
in French cooking,
each ingredient was
treated individually
to create depth of flavor
and a holistic synergy.
But the most impressive
of all of this...
tempeh!
"Tempeh"?
Yes, it is from Indonesia,
an ingredient made from
fermented soybeans.
It's fermented using bacteria
from hibiscus or banana leaves.
It is considered
a traditional food,
one that has found popularity in
the region for over 400 years.
It's so thick, but the taste
is so light and refreshing.
It's like char siu!
Texturally it is
a lot like meat.
Vegetarians and macrobians,
or anyone actively trying
to avoid meat or dairy‐related
products like to eat it.
I added a dash of soy sauce and
sake to make it teriyaki style.
Is this rich broth vegetarian?
That is correct.
It's a mixture of seaweed
and shiitake,
making it a meatless broth.
When I was overseas
a long time ago,
I stayed on at a temple,
where I met a priest who
lamented about how he had
to give up meat and fish.
He was having a
hard time with it.
I want to eat more
meat and fish!
The errors I went through
in order to make enjoyable
meatless food,
was the foundation
for this ramen creation.
Amazing. The combined umami
of the seaweed and shiitake
produced a synergistic effect.
Even without using fish
products, the result was a
solid, satisfying umami.
Wait a minute, Joichiro!
So you're saying that this dish
has no meat or fish at all,
yet you were able to
create this much richness
and depth of flavor?!
Using animal products to draw
out umami and create richness
is a process anyone can do.
But...
a thick, rich ramen
that uses no meat or fish...
That's more interesting
to the palate.
Mph.
This man's amazing.
To think, he was able to make
such a satisfying dish
by heightening the
deliciousness of soybean
and vegetables...
This bowl holds such vitality
and a wealth of ideas.
It's the very essence of a man
who's travelled the world and
seen wonders with his own eyes.
It packs a punch, but I
keep eating more and more!
It has the perfect level
of spice, so pleasing
to the tongue!
I can feel the energy
it's giving me!
It's warming me
from the inside‐out.
My cells are in
boundless rejuvenation!
The clock's
rewinding...
Rewinding!
REWINDING!
Thank you for
the delicious food!
Not that far back!
All right, it's time
for our judgment.
Phew! It was just
an illusion. Huh?!
Still, you do look
a bit younger.
[FUMIO]
Okay, judges.
Place your bowls before
who you thought made the
more delicious dish.
[FUMIO]
It's a unanimous vote.
The winner is Joichiro!
You're welcome!
[FUMIO]
Both of them made incredible
dishes with creativity
and culinary exploration,
plus a gentle push
to get the day started.
But after eating
Joichiro's dynamic ramen,
Soma's dish pales in
comparison somewhat.
[FUMIO]
Joichiro wins a
solid victory!
And Soma, your dish
was absolutely splendid.
But for me at least, I felt it
was slightly lacking.
Though it may be morning,
I'd just finished
working in
the fields.
I wanted to
eat something
more substantial.
In that respect, Chef Joichiro's
dish was robust and perfect.
I see.
My dish came in
at the bare minimum
of what they were searching
for in a gratifying meal.
But my dad thought about how to
satisfy all three of them.
To heal them to
the maximum extent.
Still, I'd say you've
gotten a bit better with
creating your dishes.
Breakfast apple risotto.
That is a pretty
innovative plate, my boy.
Hm?
Listen up, Soma:
As long as you're
here at Tohtsuki,
you'll keep
having food battles.
But don't go losing to anyone,
until you've lost to me again.
It seems cooking is how they
communicate with one another.
I swear those two are
just two peas in a pod.
All that being said...
Huh?
That makes this your 490th
consecutive loss, SO‐MA.
GRARR!
Well, that's another
victory for me.
Not having even a single
loss is gettin' kinda
boring over here.
Aah, shut up!
Wait till next time!
Um, they write it down?
ALL of their food challenges
up until now?
That seems oddly organized
for a couple of nincompoops.
[MEGUMI]
Soma has battled like
this his whole life?
Going up against his
incredibly talented father,
getting frustrated over and
over...
Oh, Soma!
I'll do my best, too!
Guh!
Huh? Okay...
Your father sure
showed what he's made of.
I guess that's the skill‐set
needed to be invited to The Ten.
Looks to be.
I was already determined
enough before, but now...
Huh?
There's unchartered lands
my dad has never explored...
And now, I feel like I really
wanna see 'em for myself
and experience all the
different ways to cook.
Well that sounds great.
All right! Let's both aim for
the Council of Ten, Megumi!
Huh? What? There's no
way I could do that!
You can and you will!
[FUMIO]
You're leaving already?
That was one of your
fastest visits yet.
Why not stay a bit
longer and give him some
more fatherly advice?
I'm not really a
hands‐on type of parent.
I'm sure he'll work
things out on his own.
You're so full of crap.
That battle was
to encourage him
to keep on moving
forward, wasn't it?
The Fall Selection
is coming up after all.
Is it?
Nah, it'd just been awhile
since I'd had the pleasure
of seeing that frustrated
look on my boy's face is all.
You still can't be
upfront with me?
Well, don't worry,
I won't hold it against you.
Plus, I needed to stop
by Tohtsuki Academy to run
a little errand of my own.
"Errand"?
Yeah, but it's nothing major.
See ya later, Ma.
Someday soon...
I'll come cook for you again.
I swear.
Even when they get older,
wanderers just never change.
[HISAKO]
I'm very sorry, Miss Erina.
I'm sure you're still tired from
enduring the training camp,
but you do have some
appointments starting today.
We'll be meeting with the owner
and head chef of Kishouan.
You'll be tasting
the new menu items
they have to offer
and afterwards meet
with the committee members
from Food Executive.
Ah! Stop the car!
Miss Erina?
Are you ok?
Yes. It was nothing.
Honestly.
[YUKI]
Huh?!
Did Joichiro seriously
leave already?
What? When did he go...?
Just a little while ago.
I don't know where that man
plans on going from here.
[SOMA]
You kidding?
He could've at least
let us see him off.
Well that blows.
I really wanted him to
try some Kyokusei eggs...
He never got the
chance to eat any.
And I was hoping
to get some advice.
I wanted to thank him
for this morning's ramen.
Ramen?
Mm‐hmm. You missed it,
Soma and his father had
a breakfast cooking battle
earlier this morning.
Why are you
so cruel to us?!
You should have
woken us up, Megumi!
Sorry! Please forgive me!
I beg you!
[YUKI]
"Sorry" won't cut it!
Oh by the way, boy...
Joichiro wanted me to
deliver you a message.
Message?
Yes.
"You need to go and
air out the shop
every once in a while."
That's it.
The shop?
[FUMIO]
Why not head back during
the upcoming vacation?
[SOMA]
Vacation, huh?
What's going to
happen to us?
Our shopping district
won't make it.
[HISAKO]
Next time on Food Wars,
the seventeenth planned course:
"Sensual Fried Chicken"
That's right.
And stick to the plan.
[JOICHIRO]
Well this sucks. I haven't
seen a car in hours.