(Sigh)
Hm? What's wrong
with you, Megumi?
Seeing and tasting
Akira's curry...
It kind of knocked the wind
out of my sails.
[AKIRA]
Curry... Oh yeah...
[MEGUMI]
It's a little more than a month
till the Selection.
Trying to come up with
a dish that will rival
one as good as Akira's
in such a short amount
of time is nearly impossible!
I don't know what I'm gonna do,
I'm freaking out!
At my family's restaurant,
back when I would watch my dad
working up close,
I hated to admit to myself,
but I knew there was still
so much I needed to improve.
And yet, he trusted me to come
up with a brand new menu item.
I was terrified.
Because I was still only
in sixth grade.
I wouldn't be able to handle
that kind of pressure!
Maybe...
But if all you do is worry about
what you need to improve on,
you'll never get anywhere.
Like right now, you know...
I've really got nothin'
to lose here,
and everything in
the world to gain.
There's no way I'm
givin' up my job at the shop,
or my food battles,
The only thing to do is
man‐up and tackle this.
Mm‐hmm!
Okay then... So spices
are gonna be important
for this theme,
of course, but I don't think
that'll be all it's about.
[MEGUMI]
It's six weeks till
the Fall Selection.
One hot summer, devoted
entirely to curry has begun.
[ISSHIKI]
HAH!
Ahh...
Hehe.
[YUKI]
"Generally, about
40 varieties of spices
are used in curries.
Of these, only 10 to 20
varieties are selected
and then blended. Huh...
I don't think you can just mix
them randomly, though,
or the individual
flavors would end up
cancelling each other out.
[MEGUMI]
Should we use the spices
whole, powdered, or raw?
I just don't know.
Plus, we have to choose
a recipe AND the oil to
draw out its aroma!
And do we use roasting
or ripening methods?
How will the ingredients
interact?
There's just too
many factors to consider!
AH!
EH?
Come back to us!
Megumi!
(Both chuckle)
Spice is important...
but it's not everything.
[KANICHI]
Seriously, this is great!
To think, a member of Bowl‐club
has made it so far!
Here's hoping one bite
of that meat of yours
sends you straight to
the main tournament,
Meat‐Meat! Wooo!
It will dramatically increase
our club's budget,
and we'll gain a ton
of new members, too!
The future of
Bowl‐club is bright!
It's not going to be
as easy as all that.
Huh?
This is about a
lot more than just
putting out some
delicious meat.
I really have to put
some thought into my
spice blend mixture.
I also need to make
sure I choose the
right kind of protein.
Meat is my thing, after all.
So I must make a
curry that maximizes
the deliciousness of the meat.
To think, you'd go so
far for Bowl‐club...
Meat‐Meat!
I couldn't care
less about that!
[TAKUMI]
You're really not going
back to Italy with me?
[ISAMI]
That's right.
Mom and Dad are gonna
be sad not seeing you.
As well as our regular
customers who always look
forward to your cooking.
I'm just putting off having to
go back a little bit longer.
I wanna see if I can work out
a few things on my own.
All right.
Well good luck.
Your goal should be
to take me down.
M'kay. But if I win, please
don't cry all over me, okay?
You're such a crybaby
whenever I beat you at stuff.
(Fighting back tears)
Hey! That was back when we were
still in elementary school!
Jeez! I'm leaving now!
Oh, Brother!
Do you have
your passport?
Can you get on the
plane by yourself?
And go to the bathroom
before you take off.
Do I need to hold your hand?
Leave. Me. Alone!
Have a good trip!
Hm.
[HEAD CHEF]
Gimme a damn break!
I don't care if she is
Head Chef Hojo's daughter,
there's no way some
daddy's little girl
is running this kitchen!
Once she steps foot
in this place,
we'll knock her on her ass
and get her outta here!
Delicious!
She's getting better.
Her cooking is far beyond
a 3rd‐year middle schooler!
Yeah. She might already be
as good as you are, Sir.
You better watch
out for her.
[MIYOKO]
Head Chef...
In three years,
I will graduate
from Tohtsuki
and return to lead
this kitchen.
Can you keep it warm
for me... "Senpai"?
One day, I'll have to enter
a battlefield stacked
deep with bullheaded men.
I'll earn prestige!
The sort of power that will
stop them from looking down on
me because of my gender.
First, I'll win the
Fall Selection,
then I'll snatch the
No. 1 seat on the Council!
I WILL make this happen.
No one can stop me.
Shut up!
You shut up!
No, you! I hate your face!
You're dumb!
[MEGUMI]
August rolled around,
and the residents of Kyokusei
started taking trips back
to their hometowns
to visit with family.
And then...
You're heading back too?
Yeah!
I wanna see
the Bon Festival,
plus I want to try combining
some of the different spices
and ingredients
from my village.
Great idea! Well, good luck.
Yeah! You, too, Soma.
It looks like you'll be the
only freshman here at the
dormitory for a while.
Yeah, but you won't
have to worry about me
getting bored around here.
See you soon.
Oh. Don't forget to
bring me a souvenir.
Mm‐hmm!
Three more weeks till
the Fall Selection.
(Sinister laugh)
Perfect...
This is the right flavor.
Now is your time.
You've had it.
Uwaahhh!
Just you wait, Hisako Arato.
(Sinister laugh)
What's the
matter, Hisako?
Uh, nothing.
I just felt a chill
for some reason.
Oh, no! Are you okay?
Should I turn down
the AC for you?
I‐I'm fine!
Don't worry, Miss Erina.
Is there anything
I can get for you?
No, please you've already
done enough by letting me
use your amazing cooking area.
Tea? Would you like me to put
some tea on for you?
No, um... I'm just fine...
I promise, I'm
really all right.
[ALICE]
Erina, I swear...
She's not competing
in the Fall Selection,
so she has nothing
but time on her hands!
True.
Since I've pretty much
decided what I'll be making,
I've got time on
my hands too.
Um, Madam?
I'd like to experiment
with my curry recipe...
Oh no! your duty is to
keep me entertained!
[FISHERMAN]
Yo!
Is that you, Megumi?!
Hey guys!
It's been a long time!
Hey, girlie, we heard
you's gonna be in
some big tournament
or somethin' or other!
It's like you're our shinin'
ray of hope 'round here!
You mean it?
Aw, c'mon, guys!
(Car honks)
Megumi!
Welcome back, sweetie!
Hey, Mom! I'm home!
Y'know, it's been a long
time since you helped us
out in the kitchen, hon.
I think you've gotten even
better.
I still have a long
way to go, Mother
I mess up
all the time,
and at training camp,
if Soma hadn't helped...
[MIYOKO]
Oh, I see.
So in the end, you just
let some man do it for you?
I thought you
were someone else.
It's just like
Miyoko Hojo said.
Someone's always coming
to my rescue.
But at Selection,
I'll need to fight on my own.
I will have to come up
with something myself.
(Yawn)
Hey, Soma.
Were you up all night?
Oh, hey there, Isshiki.
Good morning.
Ahhh... Look at all these
new dishes you've made!
Huh. This one's interesting.
Yes, it's VERY
interesting! Soma!
Yeah, but I'm just
gettin' started.
I've gotta... make
something even‐
(Snoring)
[JUN]
Oh, Akira?
Were you up
all night again?
Yeah, and I've almost
perfected it...
The blend that will
be my secret weapon.
That's no good! It's not
healthy to keep pushing
yourself like this, Akira.
You're one to talk.
I see you work through
the night all the time, Jun.
Don't call me "Jun!"
It's "Professor Shiomi" to you!
And you have a bad habit of
falling asleep on the floor.
Y'know, you're pretty heavy
for a little pipsqueak.
I was worried about you!
I hope you lose this thing!
(Door slams)
I'm not going to lose.
Jun and I together form
an unbeatable combination.
We will show them all.
I'm sorry, Akira. I
forgot to water the
plants again. You mad?
I'm not mad...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Are you really mad?
I'm NOT mad...
I knew it! You're mad!
Not. Mad!
[SOMA]
This venue is huge!
We're really gonna
cook here?
What's going on, Soma?!
Hey, Megumi!
How was your summer
vacation back home?
I wanted to try
and get ready in
my own way, but‐ Ah!
Megumi, it's
been a while!
You're looking well.
Hey, Soma!
How ya doing?
You know...
hangin' in there.
Oh, Meat‐Meat!
Uh, hey. Hi.
We're in the
same block, huh?
I'm glad to know
we're together again.
"Together"?
You idiot! We're competing
against each other!
And this time,
I'm not gonna lose!
O‐okay...
Hey...
It's a shame we
don't get to compete
in the same group as you.
But the two of us wish
you all the best
with the tournament
regardless.
Come on, Ryo,
say something deep.
'Sup, dude?
"'Sup" yourself.
The faint scent of spice is
still lingering on your fingers.
Akira!
I take it you've been
studying.
It's a good idea.
Yeah,
I wanted to feed
you a curry
that's even more
delicious than your own.
Hmph.
[TAKUMI]
Soma!
Oh, Takumi,
how you been?
Uh, I'll tell you
this once again:
Your true rival is
none other than‐
Hm? Oh, looks like
we have a new student.
Huh? What do you mean?
That's my brother.
[SOMA]
Huh?
You kidding me?!
Oh, take it easy.
[TAKUMI]
It's just the summer heat.
It always makes Isami
slim down a little.
THIS is 'cause of
the summer heat?!
Dude, I'm felling strong
as an ox; there's nothing
to worry about.
Once fall and winter
roll around,
I'll go back to my big,
beautiful, normal size.
[MEGUMI]
Really? This
happens every year?
[SOMA]
That can't
be healthy.
Anyway, you understand, right?
That is my brother!
Now as I was saying
earlier, Soma... AH!
[URARA]
Attention all attendees,
we apologize for the wait.
Please direct your
attention to the stage
in front of you.
Huh? What's going on?
Oh, sorry, can
we talk later?
Huh? Uh... hey!
The competition
will kick off
with a few words
from our principal...
Senzaemon Nakiri!
I can't believe
he's really here.
That old guy from
the opening ceremony.
AH!
(Coughing)
[URARA]
Um, Sir?
There's no need to worry.
A little something
in my throat.
Breathing in the air
in this auditorium,
one can sense, both in
body and spirit, the
drive in this building.
Even though it just
made him cough.
Shh!
This venue is also known as
the Celestial Room.
Originally, this room was only
allowed to be used
for the epic Food Wars between
the members of The Ten.
It has become tradition
that, to honor their
outstanding achievements,
we hang portraits of those who
have earned the No. 1 seat.
Woah, he's right.
There's Chef Dojima...
And Chef Kojiro Shinomiya!
He was the No. 1 seat, too?
Many battles were fought
and won in here,
and many specialties were born
and nurtured in this place.
Even now, they linger like
grains of sand.
They bring back the memories of
an unbroken chain of battles.
As was said...
The final battle
for the Fall Selection
will be held
in this auditorium.
In other words, those who make
it through prelims come back.
Yeah. There's going to be
some vicious cooking ahead.
This is your moment to shine!
The place where you will carve
out your part in history!
And so we meet
here once again...
eager participants of Tohtsuki
Academy's 92nd Selection!
(Wild cheers)
So, Takumi, what was it you
wanted to tell me earlier?
Just forget it.
Moving on,
I would like to go over
the preliminaries' rules.
Like it said in
your letters, the theme
will be curry cuisine!
The time limit is three hours.
Out of the 60 people chosen
for the preliminaries,
a total of eight will move
on to the final round.
Leaving the rest behind...
while only allowing
the best four students
from each block to proceed.
That's all that's
moving forward?!
They're gonna get rid
of that many all at once?
(Shocked murmurs)
[URARA]
A‐ and B‐block contestants,
please head to your respective
venues at this time.
The preliminaries will begin
in about one hour!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Let's go!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
I've totally got this!
Aargh! I'm so nervous,
I can't stand it!
Uh‐huh.
Yeah!
Soma!
I'll see you here again,
at the final tournament!
Yeah!
Time to begin the cooking!
Glad you could make it.
I believe I told you
that the cooking will begin
at 11 am on the dot.
Really? You say that
knowing how difficult it is
for us to find just
one minute of free time.
Are you just oblivious to fame?
So, what do you have to say?
That's Natsume Sendawara!
She's known as the
"Queen of Curry," around Japan.
She rules the curry trade here.
Eizan managed to coax me
here as a judge today,
but I doubt mere students
will be able to provide
any entertainment
to my satisfaction.
Ugh. You could've just
contributed some money.
Did you say something?
Yes. Won't you please
enjoy the Fall Selection
to your heart's
content, Madame Natsume.
I can't believe he
was able to bring out
such a major player...
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
That guy is a stud!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Yeah, and if we've got Natsume
Sendawara, Venue B must have...
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Bet you're right!
Her twin sister, Orie Sendawara!
Hey, Isshiki, my beautiful boy.
When will you finally leave this
place and join our company?
I want you to hurry up
and be my little play toy.
Hahaha! I'm still just a
young student, Madame.
Oh, that's all right!
You could drop out
of school now
and I'd make sure to look
after you forever!
[ORIE]
Think about it, Isshiki.
Think of all the scrumptious
things we could do together.
Well, for today, I hope you
can enjoy the cooking from our
brightest new freshman students.
Awww... So be it.
[ORIE]
Takumi Aldini... Is he Italian?
It seems he's using a stock of
beef shank and chicken bones.
Looks like pretty standard
fare so far.
That's his brother
right next to him...
Isami Aldini.
Hmm. Looks like he's filled
his pot with tomatoes.
Tomatoes are an essential part
of all Italian cuisine.
I'm guessing he's going
to use his background...
It only makes sense.
MMMmmm!
This aroma is enveloping
my entire body!
He's cooking the spices
in duck fat!
[AOKI and SATO]
Woohoo!
Go, Yuki!
Aha! Yeah!
Well? Just what does
she intend to make?
It's standard practice
to roast spices in oil,
but she's decided to suddenly
add water to the mixture.
Very interesting.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Check her out!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Alice Nakiri is a
completely different cook
from the others.
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
What's all that
huge equipment?
[SCHOOLBOY 4]
A blast chiller?
And a centrifuge?
I can't even imagine
what she plans on making
with those crazy gadgets!
[SCHOOLBOY 5]
Speaking of, I don't
really get what Nao
Sadatsuka's making, either.
(Sinister laugh)
[SCHOOLBOY 4]
What's in there? I can't see it.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Her roux! It's all black!
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
It looks more like
witchcraft than cooking!
Hah!
(Wild cheers)
Yeah, dude! Punish me!
Ugh! Seems like
someone's trying to
grab all the attention
from all the stupid boys!
So that's the
successor to Hojo‐Ro,
the famous restaurant in
Yokohama's Chinatown?
Y'know, several of the spices
used in Chinese cooking overlap
with those used in curry.
I look forward to seeing
how she'll utilize them.
I agree that these youngsters
are rather intriguing...
I've made my choice.
I'll take all of them,
one for each mood.
Um, what did you say?
You sound rather calm for
such a bold statement!
Oh, I guess that I
could do without that
pig‐tailed girl there.
She's unrefined and clumsy.
I don't think she stands
much of a chance.
Well, I wouldn't be so sure.
Hm?
[CHAPELLE]
She's using hua‐jiao
as an ingredient
in her recipe.
It's a spice zat will draw
out ze meat's natural aroma.
On top of that,
she's ground it coarse to
retain its rich aroma.
Excellently done!
[KANICHI]
Oh, man. You're so damn good!
WOOOO, Meat‐Meat!
He's like an obnoxious
parent cheering on his
kid at a ball game!
Just ignore him.
I wonder how the
others doing. Uh!
There's Alice Nakiri's
little helper.
I'm just about done
prepping everything.
Very well...
Hehh!
RAAAGHH!
Uh! He's completely different
than he was before!
(Wicked laugh)
Such refined knife work
being displayed.
Yes, indeed. But compared
to him, that other fellow
seems rather subdued...
[MINATOZAKA]
Is he making udon
noodles, perhaps?
That girl always tends to use
rice malt in her dishes.
She's Ryoko, right?
[IKUMI]
It's black?!
And what is that sticky stuff?
[RYOKO]
Hmph... I can do this,
even if he is favored to
win the preliminaries.
[CHAPELLE]
Fish head curry, eh?
It uses ze entire head
of a white fish,
giving ze dish a tremendous
amount of flavor.
It's a style of curry that
originated in Singapore.
[TEACHER 1]
Rather than rice,
it's accompanied by naan.
These dishes seem
kind of routine.
Hmm?
That naan, could it be...
Shh...
That's right, Jun.
My dish is just
getting started!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Oh god. That smell!
Ooh! It's like a pinch
of heavenly freshness
added to the richness of coconut
milk, makin' a dreamy blend.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
It makes me wanna start
stuffing my face!
[MINATOZAKA]
Mmm. For that scent to
suddenly fill this venue...
It's easy to tell the aroma
stewing within his pot.
I'd say he's utilized an
excellent spice blend to its
fullest potential, hasn't he?
Hmm. Well this one has quite a
different aroma altogether...
Roasted spices?!
I get. He's taken the
approach of using smoked spices
to bolster the
aroma of his dish.
The atmosphere in this building
has taken another turn!
Well... This could prove to
be somewhat interesting.
So? Who is your favorite
little freshman, Eizan?
Well. You know, uh...
It's hard to really narrow
it down, but...
there's only one cook out there
whose true skill I wish to see.
Huh?
Huh?!
Ahh! Eh?!
[IKUMI]
Soma?!
Don't tell me...
He's sleeping!
(Light snoring)
[NATSUME]
I'm Natsume.
[ORIE]
And I'm Orie.
[BOTH]
Next time on Food Wars,
the twenty‐first course:
"That Which is
Known Yet Unknown"
Get excited about it!
Why won't you
shape them
like rabbits?
Huh...?
You're so
useless!
Huh...