[P.A.]
Flight 1704 to Osaka is now
boarding on concourse E.
Now then, let's begin
the final segment of this
training camp's program.
Please, enjoy a full‐course
dinner served up by our
highly esteemed graduates.
(Cheers)
MMMmmm!
[P.A.]
Attention all students:
please collect your luggage
and board your assigned buses.
Be sure to return your room
keys to the front desk.
And please double check you've
left nothing behind.
[YUKI]
Mmmm! Yes!
Finally it's all done!
And all of us managed
to make it out.
Yeah!
Totes!
It almost seems like it
was over before it started!
True enough.
It sure was tough, though.
[YUKI]
Got that right!
Was it really necessary
for everyone
to meet up in my room
every single freaking night?
Come on, you know you
had a good time too!
Gah!
(Snoring)
You had fun last night,
I saw you...
Go on and draw.
The old maid's waiting!
Let's pick up
this game later!
[ZENJI] What?!
[SATO] Totally, we can
invite Issihiki.
[AOKI]
And we'll start a new game!
[SOMA]
Chef Kojiro Shinomiya!
So you both
made it, huh?
Yeah, we still seem
to be standing.
Chef Kojiro...
Take it you're already
heading back to France?
Yeah. I can't keep my restaurant
closed forever, y'know.
Also, I know now
what I need to do.
The next time you hear from
me, I'll have the most famous
spot in Paris,
and I'll have three stars.
There's still so much
I want to do...
It's gotten to where having
the Brousse‐Poiret Award
just isn't enough anymore.
Know what I mean?
Three stars...
Amazing!
No Japanese chef
working in France
has ever been awarded
three stars before!
Not yet...
No, no, NOO!
Urgh!
I will not let you
just leave us all
for France again!
What are you talking about,
you insane woman?
Hey, listen here, kid.
Are you interested
in Italian cooking?
Um, Megumi... I think your
skills might grow a great deal
at a sushi restaurant‐
Oh, NO!
I am taking Megumi
back with me
and treating her right!
Wh‐what?
Well... I see they've
gotten to you already.
Uh, Chef Dojima!
What's going on?!
Well this is part
of your assessment.
What assessment?
This training camp also allows
us to recruit some new personnel
once they've graduated
from Tohtsuki academy.
Some former graduates will take
time off from their restaurants
and come to work as sous‐chefs
adding to their skill‐set.
This serves as a place where
chefs can recruit new talent.
[SENA]
Finding promising chefs
is not an easy task.
So this is a good way to search.
Ooh, that makes sense.
Is that what the training
camp was about all along?
Check it out. Megumi
still doesn't get why
those chefs are trying
to recruit her.
Mm‐hmm! Mm‐hmm!
Y'know Soma.
You could find your place
working at the Resort.
You're welcome here anytime.
I'm extremely honored
to hear that, but I've got
"Yukihira" to look after.
[GIN]
I see.
You already have a job
waiting for you somewhere?
Yeah! My dad and I run a small
restaurant together back home.
I'm not exactly sure where
he is right now, but...
one day, I'm sure
I'll get his approval.
I will be the chef that
keeps "Yukihira" going!
Hey, Kojiro, you're really
going for three stars?
Well somebody has to.
What do you say I go
over there and help you
accomplish that goal?
Yeah, works for me.
I'm sure I could use a new
busboy to help mop up.
What?! HEY!
Huh?!
Chef Dojima?
Is something wrong, Sir?
Uh... Of course not.
Thanks for all of your help.
Guess I'll see you
back at the dorm.
Yeah, see you later.
Oh, no! My hand towel!
[HISAKO]
What? You forgot something?
No, no, no, NO!
But we're just about to leave.
I'll go get it for you‐
It's not a problem.
I'll get it myself.
Oh, and I'll find my own
way back to the academy.
Could you be a doll and take my
luggage for me? Thank you!
[HISAKO]
O‐okay.
Thank goodness, I found it!
(Jabbering)
We sure got our fill at
Tohtsuki's Resort this time.
I'm lookin' forward
to next year!
I'm on the wrong bus...
[P.A.]
When several express buses
are gathered together,
it's quite easy to get confused.
When leaving the bus,
please be sure to remember
the vehicle number
and where it was parked.
[TOKUZO]
Oh!
You're the one who
made the wonderful
souffle omelets.
Ah! You're the egg man!
[TOKUZO]
That was exceptionally
done, young man.
[SOMA]
Uh...
I wasted so many eggs!
I'm sorry, Sir!
Hmm...
That's fine by me...
So long as after you
graduate, you plan on
using Tokuzo Brand eggs.
For the restaurant you'll
surely one day own, right?
Right!
And you must promise to
use my green beans too!
And of course
my cheese, as well.
Want some rice crackers,
young man?
Here, have some candy.
Ah, thank you.
Thanks very much. Thanks.
Look, people! I don't really
have the time for this, okay!
Where's my bus?!
Uh... Um...
They left me!
For real?
I survive the whole training
camp from hell
just to go out like this?
Ah! Why are you
still here?!
Aw, you care?
Well this and that happened,
and the next thing you know
there was the bus...
Miss Erina!
We were able to arrange
a car for you.
Luckily there was
still one left in the
parking garage. Oh!
[STAFF]
Did you miss the bus
as well, young man?
Want some rice crackers?
I don't eat those.
Some candy?
Are you serious?
Come to think of it...
You said you looked forward
to seeing me fail
one of these days,
didn't you?
But it looks like you
can't get rid of me, can ya?
I am not even going to look
at his stupid smug face!
HEHEHEHEHE!
Go ahead, keep floundering
around on the edge if you want.
There's no way you'll be picked
to be a member of the Selection.
"Selection"?
You don't even know
what that is.
It's Tohtsuki's legendary...
?Fall Selection.
It's a festival where the chosen
few
show their skills in a battle of
fine cuisine.
It's the first opportunity
for students to display
their abilities off campus,
in front of the academy's
directors and investors, all
gathered in the same place.
The screening process
has already begun.
Of course you
didn't even notice.
Members of the
selection committee were
evaluating us at the camp.
Oh, yeah!
Those guys that were
wearing the suits...
You see, the goal of this
training camp
wasn't just the means
to weed people out...
The intention was to determine
which students were fit
to move up the ranks.
A festival of fine cuisine, huh?
That sounds like
it could be fun!
Now I could really get
behind something like that.
There is no way they'll ever
choose you for something
as elite as this!
What's your deal anyway?
And the things you say...
I gained the experience that
comes from messing up.
You think you're gaining
experience from "messing up"?
You're simply making
excuses for yourself!
For a chef, failure
is unacceptable!
I don't know...
I do know!
Only the most exceptional dishes
should grace the dining table
of culinary establishments...
It is the essence
of haute cuisine!
There's one chef who knows...
Huh? What was that?
Don't worry about it.
So, uh, hey, Erina...
what was your excuse
for missing the bus?
Keep your nose out of my
business thank you very much.
Okay...
This is, uh...
pretty awkward.
Maybe I'll just sleep.
(Snoring)
There it is!
Oh thank goodness.
Well, well, well...
So, Joichiro...
Soma Yukihira is your son.
[FUMIO]
Back and forth, back and forth.
Cleany clean!
Spick and span,
squeaky clean!
Doo dee doo...
Woo! That training camp
should be over soon.
Things should perk up
around here again.
(Doorbell)
You kids certainly got back
faster than I thought...
you... would.
Well, honestly.
If you're going to show up...
you could've at least
called before gracing
me with your presence.
Still no common sense, eh, boy?
Well, I found myself
in the area...
I'm back.
[JOICHIRO]
Heh heh, heh heh, heh heh heh!
[SOMA]
Hey, we're back!
[AOKI]
We're back!
(Laughter)
[ISSHIKI]
Soma, did you really
come back
in one of those
hotel limos?
[YUKI]
Woo! Must be nice!
You're a VIP!
[SOMA]
Nah, c'mon, that's not true.
Anyway, for what it's worth,
I'm glad you all made it
back in one piece.
I'm sure that you
are all exhausted.
So for tonight, you are all
going to be treated to a feast.
(Cheers)
Bring it on!
Yeah it's been awhile since
you've cooked for us.
Simmer down. I'm not the one
who'll be cooking for you.
Huh?
Hey, Soma. Welcome back.
Come lend me a hand.
Sure.
Handle the mise en place,
would you?
I've already made the stock.
Mm‐hm, right,
you got it.
Wait a minute! You can't just
show up all of a sudden
like it's no big deal!
What are you even doing here?!
How do you two
know each other?
Uh, who is he?
He's an academy graduate. And
a former resident of Kyokusei
A graduate of Tohtsuki?!
Well, quite the generation
gap we have here.
Former No. 2 Seat on The Ten...
I give you Joichiro Saiba.
Former No. 2 seat on the Ten?!
"Saiba"?
Ah, the rice looks to be
just about ready, Soma.
Who cares about the rice?! Just
tell me what's going on, Dad!
They're father and son?!
Ahh, that makes sense!
[SOMA]
My dad's a Tohtsuki graduate...
He lived at Kyokusei...
And he was on the Ten... Heh!
This seems to be harder than
I thought to try and process.
It's a lot to take in.
Whoa! Soma's
actually flustered!
[RYOKO]
He's Soma's father, all right...
there's no doubt about that.
So lemme get this straight.
You're Joichiro Saiba?
Hey. You know of me, do ya?
Of course. I've seen your
name mentioned a few times
throughout some old
documents I've read.
You're the "Wandering Chef,"
who's traveled far‐and‐wide
and proven himself at famous
restaurants across the globe.
But one day, you
suddenly disappeared
from the culinary world.
To those in the know,
you're a legend.
And my name is
Satoshi Isshiki.
I am the current No. 7 seat.
It's an honor to meet
the great Joichiro Saiba.
Eheh... I go by the name
"Yukihira" nowadays.
Or you can just
call me "Joichiro."
Uh, he hasn't even
batted an eye at how
Isshiki is dressed!
That's a former
member for you.
I'm not sure that's
the issue here.
I can't believe my dad's really
that famous around here.
How could you possibly
not know any of this?!
Well I only
recently found out
that he would pick up
work overseas every
now and then.
[PHONE]
Blah blah blah...
For some reason,
he'd get phone calls
in a language I
didn't understand.
And there were a lot
of photos of foreigners
hanging out with my dad.
But come on, isn't
that sort of thing pretty
commonplace in every household?
Not commonplace
anywhere!
To think, Soma's father is
someone so famous...
All right!
Shall we make a toast?!
(All agree and cheer)
[FUMIO]
To everyone who's
made it through
the training camp
from hell!
Today you will eat
and drink your fill!
Thank you so much for the food!
Cheers, everyone!
A meal made by a
former seat of The Ten!
Can't wait to
see how it tastes!
It makes me kinda nervous!
(Fluttered breath)
Here you are. Enjoy the food.
O... kay...
It's a beautiful landscape...
I've never been to a
place like that before!
It's like a whole new world!
[ALL]
This flavor is so...
ARABIAN!
[AOKI and SATO]
This is super delish!
May I ask about the paste
you put on this lamb?
What is it?
[JOICHIRO]
That's harissa.
It's an all‐purpose
condiment from North Africa
made from hot peppers
and other ingredients.
I also took a page
from traditional
Middle Eastern cooking
and added parsley
and garam masala.
Haahhh!
So, um, Mister Joichiro,
what is this dish called?
[JOICHIRO]
That's zuppa di pesce.
It's a Ligurian‐style seafood
soup that uses stockfish.
Mister Joichiro!
What is this?
And, uh, tell me about this!
Oh that's a good one.
Mister Joichiro...
seems like one of those real
men you hear rumors about!
Yes. He is so
grown‐up and handsome.
Can't you kinda see
that in his son too?
You think,
in the future...
Soma could end up like that?
(Fawn)
Wha?
What the heck?
They were all so down‐trodden,
but the second they tasted his
food, their hearts were warmed.
This cooking just
brims with the personality
of the man who made it!
Woohoo! This is so good,
I can't stand it!
Oh man! Everything is
like the best thing ever!
What about this one here?
Haha...
GOD!
[JOICHIRO]
Oh, that?
I tried replicating a snake
dish I ate last month.
Yeah, it's disgusting.
You chop it up with
the skin still on,
then boil it without
prepping it at all.
This is some seriously
heinous food.
Oh yeah? You think
it's horrible enough
to get into my Best Ten?
Maybe up to No. 4?
[SHUN]
If it's horrible, shouldn't
it be the "Worst Ten"?
I think it could even be No. 2!
[YUKI] Yeah, they're father
and son, all right.
Nah, No. 2 is gonna
be hard to beat.
Joichiro...
you loved your bizarre
and unsightly foods...
and you always did.
Hm?
You were the man
they once called
"Carnage," after all.
[FUMIO]
But now... You seem to
have become quite adept
at making considerate dishes.
Huh?
[FUMIO]
You should let Gin
taste this sometime.
[JOICHIRO]
Yeah, you're right.
Gin? Wait a sec, don't tell me!
Yes. I'm sure he put on lots
of airs at the training camp.
Executive Chef of
Tohtsuki Resort, Gin Dojima.
[FUMIO]
So. This one is Gin.
And this is Joichiro.
Back when they were sophomores
in the high school division.
(Girls fawn)
They're both so young cute!
Come on, Ma, you don't
need to keep showing
them stuff like that.
Oh, what's the harm in it?
So Chef Dojima was a resident
of Kyokusei Dorm, too?
Seriously?
Gin was the No. 1 seat
on the Ten.
And Joichiro was the No. 2 seat.
Back then those two ushered
in the golden age of Kyokusei
as I came to know and love it.
They won countless Food Wars,
snatching up land and
expanding the dorm's grounds,
contributing funds to improve
the dorm's kitchen,
and even securing supply routes.
They paid for it with what
they'd won through their own
strengths.
[JOICHIRO]
We were getting to where
we could practically
form our own country!
[FUMIO]
That field you all plowed,
your dedicated malted rice area,
and even the chicken coop...
Gin and Joichiro had a direct
hand in the bringing of ALL of
that to the Kyokusei dorm.
And every year...
Gin never fails to send
me a New Year's card or
some sort of gift.
(Clears throat)
SOME people don't
even bother
to send me a letter
once in a while.
Well that's the reason
why I come and visit
you sometimes, Ma.
[FUMIO]
Oh don't even!
You drop in unexpectedly and
leave whenever you feel like it.
(Joichiro laughs)
Truly, some legendary
Tohtsuki graduates.
Well, I never actually
graduated the Academy.
No way! How's that possible?
You were the No. 2 chair.
A lot can happen.
So did Gin seem like
he's doing well?
Huh? I guess.
Hey, Dad...
This place...
Kyokusei Dormitory...
What was it like
for you living here?
Hmph! I had a blast.
Everyone brushing up
on their cooking skills,
in whatever way they liked...
Hey, Dad...
You wanna crash
in my room tonight?
Yeah, well...
Huh?
Ha! Soma, you're in Room 303?
Huh? Yeah, that's right.
Right in the middle
of that room...
there's a stain from
a spilt pot of stew...
I was cooking up
there one night.
[JOICHIRO]
Hey, Ma! Let me
borrow an empty room!
[FUMIO]
Okay!
My dad was here...
in this room?
Joichiro Saiba, huh?
Really?
just when you think
you know someone.
You find out... there's
so much more to them.
[JOICHIRO]
Soma! Soma!
You up?
Yeah.
I'm in the kitchen right now.
Come on down here,
and bring your knife.
(Groan)
Guess I'm helping
with breakfast, huh?
[SOMA]
Come to think of it,
why did my dad even come
back to Japan?
Was it for a job
or something?
Hey! There he is!
Have you kept your
knife good'n sharp?
Of course. Yesterday,
to get rid of the smell
of the sharpening stone, I‐
Okay, fine.
Sorry to throw you right
into this
without warning, but I wanna
see how far you've come along.
Or how far you may
have fallen behind.
Show me right here and now.
I'd say it's been too
long since we've had a
proper food battle...
Now show me.
[JOICHIRO]
Next time on Food Wars,
it's the sixteenth course.
Sorry for the wait.
"The Cook Who Traveled
Thousands of Miles"
Please enjoy.
Nuts to you...
Nuts to you!
NUTS NUTS NUTS NUTS NUTS!