[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Hey, you guys gettin' hungry?
Wanna get some ice cream?
Nah, I need
something more filling!
[AKI]
Me too! I'm
starving over here!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Yeah I get that, but what
are you in the mood for?
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Meat!
[AKI]
That sounds great!
I, like, want me
some meat!
Why don't you take
a little bite?
It's fried peanut butter
squid tentacles.
It's so putrid,
you're gonna freak.
AHHmm!
(Peanut‐buttery cries)
No, please!
[AKI]
Every single day...
You look at that place
whenever we pass by.
Huh?! N‐not really...
Don't you
"not really" me!
I totally know you're
thinking about Soma again.
You should've told
him how you felt
while you were still gushing
over him in middle school.
Or at least when you
learned he was going off
to his fancy cooking school.
Uhhh...
Ah, no no! I'm sorry!
I didn't mean it
like that, Mayu!
Anyway, look, I don't
think it's too late
for you to go after him.
Maybe you should
try calling him
or, like, sending
a text or something.
But I...
I'm nothing special.
He would never
notice me.
Uh... Oh, uh, hey there,
Mayumi, how's it hanging?
Ahhh!
[BOYS] WOAH!
[AKI] Omigod, when
did you get here?!
Hey, it's been a while,
you guys.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
You should've told us
you were coming back!
You gonna reopen
the shop?
Nah, uh, I just
came to air the
place out for my dad.
WOOAAH!
"Yukihira" is open again!
What?!
A dream come true!
C'mon, Soma, please! You
gotta make me something!
I'm hungry too!
And me!
And me, too, please!
I've missed this
place's food so much!
Heh! 'Kay. I'll get to
prepping right away, folks.
Eatery "Yukihira":
reopened for a limited time!
Yeah!
(Restaurant chatter)
One oyako bowl and
a tofu special!
Yahoo!
I've been craving this!
Where's your
dad been, Soma?
Haven't seen him around.
Well, he was back in
town a while ago...
Think he maybe went
overseas again or something.
Hey Soma!
Can I get a side
of fried sprouts?
Coming!
Ah, Soma...
What? A cooking battle?
Yeah, he's gonna
go up against his dad
and, like, he wants
us to judge it.
You've never been to the
Yukihira restaurant, have you?
The food there is
TOTALLY super amazing!
You really don't
want to miss out on this.
Soma and I have shared classes
since kindergarten,
but we've never really
spoken all that much.
Bon Appetite, my lady!
Thank you very much!
(Squeals)
I don't really have
any skills or hobbies.
We don't have
much in common.
Hah!
[MAYU]
To me, Soma Yukihira
truly is amazing.
It's only been about
two months since we
graduated middle school,
but he seems so
much more grownup now.
It's like he's gotten even
more unreachable for me...
[CUSTOMER 1]
Thanks for the food!
[CUSTOMER 2]
Thanks, that was great!
See you later!
[SOMA]
Thanks, guys!
That's weird, it's kinda
dead out there.
Normally, it'd be
pretty busy by now.
Wonder what's going on.
(Loud sigh)
Gah!
[SOMA]
Is everything okay
with you, Mr. Tomita?
Does big business really
have that much power?!
Tomi, you need
to calm down.
What's wrong, has something
happened, Mr. Tomita?
The truth is, one month ago
the station's commercial area
finally reopened after
some major renovations.
[SOMA]
Oh, yeah, it looks great, huh?
[TOMITA]
Well, they beefed up their
"station shopping experience."
They've got clothing stores,
book stores, all sorts of
different boutiques.
But what's getting
the most buzz is this
fried chicken place.
Word is it's
really something!
Yeah?
So have you guys
tried it out already?
Uh‐huh. Yeah my parents
just bought some the other day.
Us too. Saw their
commercial on the internet.
Yeah, I hear it's been
getting a lot of views!
(Music playing)
It's crispy,
but oh so juicy!
One, two...
Unbelievable!
10 out of 10 taste score!
We keep losing customers.
All because they're going
over there for their fancy,
juicy fried chicken!
People coming from work, from
school...
They just pass on by.
My boxed lunch shop's
in trouble!
At this rate,
who knows how long
I can stay in business?
That's sad.
This isn't the time
to eat and sulk.
More, please.
No!
I guess it's the sign of
the times around here.
We gotta face the facts,
our area is done for.
Okay, I'm gonna try something.
"Try something"? Like?
Their main draw is
fried chicken, right?
Well we're gonna come up with
a new kind of fried chicken,
one that will out‐juicy
their juiciest.
What?! That's crazy, Soma!
We are totally
outclassed here!
In funds AND
customer appeal!
Those guys are villains!
But it's better than
sittin' here doing nothin'.
Uhhh...
Customers tend to get greedy
when they want something.
"Yukihira" is open again!
C'mon, Soma, please!
You gotta make me something!
If something's really good,
they're sure to take notice.
(Cats meowing)
I'm part of this
shopping area, too.
I can't just let it go downhill.
I'll do what it takes to get
this place hoppin' again!
Let's make a new kind
of fried chicken!
Ohhh!
I like your thinking, Soma!
He's definitely
Yukihira's son, alright!
It just might work!
Here's the plan:
I'm gonna use
all my time off
to make the ultimate
fried chicken!
[SOMA]
There's a lot
of prep work to do!
So there's no time to waste.
[SHAVED HEAD]
Let us know if you
need anything.
[TOMITA]
It's not like
we're very busy!
[BLACK HAIR]
We're all counting on you, Soma!
[AKI]
Um, yeah, that's a face that
says you want to help him out,
but you totally don't feel
like there's anything you can
do that's useful...
You're, like,
SO obvious.
I mean you need
some mental help, girl.
Aha! Hey, Soma! Shouldn't
you have a taste tester?
Hmm?
This girl here doesn't have any
conflicts or club activities
and she happens to have a really
great sense of taste!
Uh...
Ah, what're you doing?!
I don't know a thing about
being a proper taste tester!
Well an amateur's opinion
could actually be pretty
useful at a time like this.
But Aki, I'm just a‐
HYA!
"Ooh, I'd love
to help."
Oh. Well, I do appreciate
the offer, Mayumi.
First, we've gotta check out
their fried chicken.
That'll give us a clue as
to how to make our new dish.
"Yeah, right!"
[SOMA]
Great. I'll see
you tomorrow morning.
"Uh‐huh!"
[MAYU] (Sigh)
Can I do this?
I'm not so sure.
I'm not qualified to judge
something like this...
Oh don't be silly.
You've already judged for one
of his cooking battles!
That's totally different!
This is going to be an
important new menu item, okay!
You listen to me!
This is your big chance, Mayu!
A man and woman
with the same goal,
working in close quarters...
Aaah!
They're sure to get super close
and intimate with each other!
G‐g‐g‐get close?
Do not screw this up!
You hear me?!
Aki, you're scaring me!
Fried chicken, huh?
I've made it here
plenty of times, but...
like that buffet challenge
at the training camp,
there might be more
to it, something to
do with the takeout.
Who out of my friends would
know something about that?
Fried chicken...
(Jiggle)
Chicken meat...
Meat!
(Phone ringing)
Ugh. Who the hell could that be?
I'm tryin' to enjoy my
vacation time over here, people!
What in the...? That's weird.
I don't think I've ever
seen this number before.
Who is this?
Hey, Meat‐Meat. It's Soma!
How did you get my number?!
Oh uh, sorry about that,
I asked Kanichi to tell me.
Okay, so, what do
you want, Soma?
I'm kinda in a hurry to
create a new spectacular
fried chicken dish.
I'm in my hometown right now,
but I was wondering if you'd be
able to come and help me out.
Huh? You want me to
come to your house?
Are you too busy?
No! I, uh, mean YES.
I'm sure I can find time to
help out a classmate.
Still, I'm SO busy over here.
My goodness, does the time fly!
I guess it can't be helped,
y'know, so busy...
If you're too busy,
I can ask someone else.
I JUST SAID I'LL DO IT! AHHHH!
Um... Uh...
(Boing)
(Pow)
(Sheen)
Creepy. This whole
area looks deserted.
Let's see...
"Japanese Eatery 'Yukihira.'"
Where are you?
Maybe I should have dressed in a
bit more conservative fashion.
No, no! I won't let society
rule me I gotta be me!
[SOMA]
Sorry, Mayumi!
Just a bit
longer, okay?
S‐sure! I'm fine!
Take your time!
Oh my God! I'm so nervous!
I wonder if I'll be able
to help at all.
You better get close!
You gotta get all
up in there, Mayu!
Don't pressure me like
this, you're seriously
stressing me out!
Hello?
AHHHH!
This is the Yukihira
restaurant, right?
Is, uh, Soma here?
Uh... um yes.
[SOMA]
Oh, Meat‐Meat!
Thanks for coming all this way.
Oh, so I see you've
already met my friend Mayumi
from middle school.
She's gonna be
our taste‐tester.
Huh?
This is one of my fellow
high‐school students.
She is our resident
meat expert.
You can call her
"Meat‐Meat."
Meat‐Meat?
Will you stop telling people
about that stupid nickname!
I will cut you!
Come on, where's
your team spirit?
The gang's all here.
Let's go check out the enemy!
[KINU]
Hello, hello! Welcome folks!
Try the famous fried chicken
making news all over town.
(Laughter)
(Cackle)
Ahhhh! What should I wear?
Maybe I should go
with something daring.
Can I just go in
there being myself?
No! Aagh, son of a...!
Whoa! It's gotten
so big!
It's kinda fancy, too.
Our shopping district doesn't
stand a chance against somethin'
like this, huh? (Laughs)
Um. That's nothing
to laugh about, Soma.
Crap! It's not like I imagined
being all alone with him at his
house or anything.
I only came to think up
a new menu item!
So Soma called her,
"Meat Meat?"
[MAYU]
She looks like a model.
(Men fawning)
I've never seen
someone so... so sexy.
I don't even know how
to look at her.
I am so far out
of that league.
Okay so...
There's nothing weird about
someone else being here.
And yet, why am I so
ticked off?!
Soma said she's his childhood
friend or something.
(Mayu laughing)
Is THIS his type?
Is that really it?
Ah! Don't tell me...
Ms. Meat‐Meat is
Soma's girlfriend!
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE LOOKING AT,
LITTLE GIRL?!
I‐I'm sorry!
Hey stop picking
on Mayumi, Meat‐Meat.
Leave her alone.
Quit callin' me freakin'
"Meat‐Meat"!
Uh did I bother you
on your day off?
Um, no, not really.
Sorry about that, Mayumi.
Uhuhuhuh!
Hm. This is their
first time to meet.
I need to try to
help them get along.
Is that it?
The famous fried chicken?
[KINU]
Please line up right over here.
Welcome to "Mozuya," Fried
Chicken Specialty Shop!"
Sorry for the wait.
[KINU]
Our special right now is the
12‐piece combination, folks.
Take some home and
be a family hero!
Wait, so this fried
chicken place is a Mozuya?
You've heard of it?
It's really popular all over
the Kansai area these days.
We have three types of chicken:
And that woman right
there is Kinu Nakamozu.
normal, spicy, and super spicy!
She's at the top of the Mozuya
chain of command at the moment.
They built up their brand
after winning the gold medal
in the All‐Japan Fried
Chicken Championship
three years in a row.
They're said to be a shoo‐in
for this year, too.
I get it now...
[SOMA]
A lot of customers are
housewives, huh?
Mm‐hm. And it
gets even busier
at night, too.
The packaging is stylish,
so it's especially
popular with women.
They say a lot of people will
take the train here from other
stations.
Please, right this
way, everyone.
[SOMA]
They've got a great
storefront
and lots of staff.
They sure are busy...
Mr. Tomita?!
Huh?
Hey, Soma!
What are you doing?
Well, uh,
I thought maybe
I could help you
out in some way.
What's with the disguise?
We are deep into
enemy territory.
It would be dangerous for them
to know who I am.
How so?
You need to be careful, Soma.
[KINU]
You don't have to be
all sneaky, you know.
Why not stand proudly in line
like everyone else?
Or are you too
scared to be seen?
EEEHHH! AAAAHHHH!
Oh my, are these your friends
from the shopping district?
How cute!
Here kiddos, give it a try!
[SOMA]
You're okay with that?
Well then...
Don't mind if I do.
The batter is very
lightly fried,
and the chicken inside is plump
and bursting with flavor.
It runs wild on the tongue!
It's like a flurry of arrows
hitting you with waves of
deliciousness!
(Cackle)
That is really incredible!
How is it so tasty and juicy?
Oh, about that...
We exclusively use locally
produced Omi chicken,
which are top‐of‐the‐line
and fed only organic herbs.
But the clincher is our
marinade,
which uses Mozuya's unique,
signature soy sauce as a base.
To that we add grated apple and
ten separate spices,
giving the chicken
a thorough flavor profile.
Then we use an OPEN fryer to
get it golden and crispy!
"It's the best fried
chicken anywhere!"
Well at least that's what
all the magazines tell us.
Is it ok for you
to blab like this?
This is an enemy recon
mission after all.
Oh no! No worries!
I mean it's not like YOU
could ever possibly make
something like this. (Laughs)
Oh dear, what a sad
little man‐child,
having girls and children
do the dirty work for you...
You just sat around licking
your wounds, while customers
stopped coming to your shop.
You don't have a shred of pride
or purpose about you!
If a shady little urchin
like you were lurking outside,
it would most definitely
drive away any potential
customers, amiright?!
This man's incompetence
reminds me of someone...
You are the next Don
of Bowl‐club, Meat‐Meat!
You're pretty confident
teasing this man.
What would you say...
if our shopping area could
make a fried chicken
more delicious than yours...
Mozuya would be
totally disgraced!
Riight?
You sure do talk a big
game there, little boy.
But talking's a lot easier
than cooking, isn't it?
What're you gonna do, punk?
I can't hear you!
Yeah... Your dried‐up,
pissant shopping district
has no sense of identity
or competitiveness.
It is only natural
that it would fail!
But you're always welcome
here at Mozuya when you
want some quality cuisine.
See ya next
time, kids.
(Theme Song)
♪Fried chicken,
fried chicken Mo‐zu‐ya!♪
[KINU]
Thank you! Buh‐bye!
Um... that was, uh,
pretty terrifying!
Like some horrible scene
in a yakuza movie!
So you really want to try
making the enemy's version
of their own fried chicken?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
Neither of them
seem fazed by any of this.
They're so focused!
Let's get started on making
something to take down Mozuya!
I'll cut the breast meat
in uneven chunks...
And let it rest in
some marinade...
[IKUMI]
I added grated apple and
onion, the same kinds
of things as Mozuya.
I mixed it up by
adding ginger, as well.
That'll form the base
of our flavors.
[SOMA]
Then, coat the meat thoroughly
and let it marinate some more.
This is just a trial run so
I'll fry it up soon,
but my guess is Mozuya
lets their meat marinate
for about 10 hours or more.
Ten hours or more?
That's a long time!
[SOMA]
Okay, now we coat all the
meat with potato starch.
Slapping off excess starch
is the key to getting it nice
and crispy.
I never knew that...
I just thought that the more you
had on the tastier it would be.
[SOMA]
Alright, the temperature's
perfect. Let's try it out!
Trial dish No. 1 is done!
Mayumi, give it a taste!
Okay!
(Crispy moan)
Oh wow, this is SO
delicious, Soma!
It's not quite right...
it doesn't have the same
kind of punch
that Mozuya's chicken does.
It's that top‐shelf marinade.
It has soy sauce, garlic,
and a bunch of different
seasonings.
Combining all that umami gives
it layers of flavor.
I'm sure they spent a lot
of years getting it just right.
How do we go up against
a marinade like that?
I think I've got it!
We don't have to
necessarily fight them
with fried chicken, do we?
We could use beef or pork...
We've got tons of
options to work with!
Hmm... You have a point there.
What about using
some A5‐grade beef?
Mph!
[IKUMI]
That would surely trounce
them in both quality
and word‐of‐mouth!
But that's super expensive
meat, isn't it?
As a member of the Mito Group,
I can give you a discount.
Call it a favor
as a classmate.
You'll get it wholesale
so you can have the best
ingredients to fight with!
Hold on a sec. Let me crunch
some numbers right quick...
Thank you, Meat‐Meat,
this is a big help.
If you could come up with 100
grams for about 1,000 yen...
A hundred grams for 3,500 yen!
Um, no. Thanks anyway.
Huh? That's super low,
so don't try to cheap out now!
It's not a matter of
being cheap back...
You got any good ideas, Mayumi?
Huh? Um, well...
I dunno... um...
S‐something that's unique to
this shopping area.
But I don't have
any specific ideas!
I'm really sorry.
I'm not much help.
[KINU](Laughs)
Customers are coming to the
station by both train and bus...
And while they're here,
they take advantage of
the station's facilities...
This location is tremendous.
Sure enough, opening this
storefront was the right idea.
Well, given it was YOU who
advised us to expand into
Kanto...
I'd say it's only natural.
We're doing so well, I mean.
Don't let your guard down.
The Mozuya brand
isn't recognized in
the Kanto area yet.
If you get wind of something,
let me know at once.
You sure worry a lot
for such a youngster!
Everything's going
to be perfect.
Assess market trends and
continue taking optimal
measures.
That's the golden rule
of business.
Um, well if I had to
say something...
it's that some kid from the
shopping area came 'round
talking nonsense.
What kid?
It's nothing to worry about.
He's no threat to us, the shop
is flooded with customers!
It's just a matter of time
before Mozuya dominates
throughout the entire area!
Just to be safe, I want you to
keep an eye out for him.
And continue to report in.
Understand?
Yeah, sure thing.
Grrr... How many of
these uppity brats
do I have to deal
with in one day?
[IKUMI]
Hmm. None of them
are BAD per se,
they're just kinda normal.
We've already tried
different seasonings
and changing up
the batter consistency.
Nothing's jumping off
the plate, is it?
So what do we change?
What kind of fried chicken
would win back our customers?
We need something
to differentiate us
from the other guys.
(Sigh)
[GUY 1]
Come on, guys!
What do you wanna eat?
[IKUMI]
Wait... Students pass by
even while on vacation.
Lots of them, too.
They're coming back
from their club activities.
There are a lot
of schools around here.
We've got high school
and college kids...
S‐something that's unique to
this shopping area.
I've got it!
Huh? What do
you mean, Soma?
Oh, man, I've been such
a bonehead about this!
We don't have to fight the
enemy on their own terms!
So we're going with the
A5 beef after all?!
Nah, we're still going
with the fried chicken.
Um, but didn't you just say
you didn't want to fight
them at their own game?
And we're not going to.
We'll use the same thing, but
we'll do something they can't.
Something so unique that
only we can provide it.
A way to make eating
fried chicken better
than it's ever been...
Heh!
We'll create something
specific to this area...
The deciding factor
in this battle! Hehe.
[EIZAN]
You'll do what
I say without question.
I'll consult for you
only on that condition.
Good, I'll do it.
Heh. It's not just Mozuya.
Everyone's after my
magic touch...
[ISSHIKI]
It's almost time.
Yes yes. I'm well
aware of that.
What's on
today's agenda?
Didn't you look
at the notice?
It's the Fall
Selection.
We have to go through
the first‐years and whittle
down the candidates.
But you know that.
Yeah, but seriously...
Why do we have to bother with
this on our vacation time?
[ISSHIKI]
Well, it can't be helped.
This is an important
responsibility...
for Tohtsuki's Council of Ten.
(Theme Song)
♪Mozu, mozu mozu mozu...♪
[KINU]
Next time, it's fried
chicken in the station!
Mozuya, Mozuya, Mozuya, folks!
"The Fried Chicken of Youth"
You know you wanna
give it a try!
And keep on coming
back to Mozuya!
(Maniacal laugh)