[ERINA]
Objection!
We cannot choose this student.
This judgment should
be reviewed.
His behavior is completely
unacceptable for a time‐honored
tribute to fine cuisine.
Um, Erina... When it comes
to cooking, your opinions
are generally correct...
But for some reason,
when it comes to Soma,
you become illogical and aren't
capable of listening to reason.
Uh!
I wonder... Did something
happen between you?
Something private?
Um! Not at all!
I simply don't feel that he's
qualified for such an honor!
Um, Isshiki!
Could it be...
you're giving favorable
treatment to the underclassmen
in your dorm?
Hahaha! Oh no, not at all.
[EIZAN]
Soma Yukihira...
The boy is a
tricky little story.
I support this choice.
True, he's accomplished
very little here at school.
And his entry into Tohtsuki
was rather questionable.
See a few of you at graduation!
[EIZAN]
But at the camp,
he showed great initiative
at the 11th hour and
cleared 200 servings.
He received high praise
even on the first day's
challenge.
Wouldn't such an
unconventional student
invigorate our festival
just that much more?
Why you're dissatisfied with
this candidate is beyond me.
Okay then... he's in.
[ISSHIKI]
There're no objections and
the decision is final.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Hey, hurry!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
They're gonna post the
announcements!
(Cheers)
Aw yeah!
Aw, dammit!
These are the students who'll
be in the Fall Selection.
I did it!
Ow!
[RYOKO]
Yuki! Get...off...me!
Uh, what now? Help me.
OW!
[SOMA]
Hey!
Did you three get chosen
for Fall Selection too?
Sure did!
Sweet, that's pretty awesome.
Even before
a Food War...
I've been given
the chance to battle
you directly, Soma!
Hey, Meat‐Meat!
Did you make
the cut?
Y‐yeah.
I take it
you did, too?
Oh, and good luck
to you, Takumi.
Hey! I don't need you to
placate me you, piece of crap!
Quit laughing!
What are you lookin at?!
(Giggle)
Like it wasn't going to happen.
Let's see...
Ah, there's my name
written right over there.
Of course it is, dummy!
If you hadn't been chosen,
you would've been
an embarrassment as
my intimidating aide.
And I forbid you to
get eliminated in the
preliminary round.
Don't worry about it.
I'm prepared to put up
a fight till the end,
even if it means I have
to go up against you to win.
What's happening
to your face?
What the heck
is wrong with you?
It wouldn't hurt for you to show
me some respect once in awhile.
[RYO]
But I always
show you respect.
More! Respect me more!
You need to be like
Erina's secretary!
She grovels like a pro.
Oh, it's Erina's
cousin! Hey!
Oh, hey there!
How are you, Soma?
Hope everything's swell.
Looks like Soma is
getting to know
all the campus big
shots, isn't he?
He's friends with
them already?
Yeah! I have to tell
Miss Fumio all about it!
It sure would make her
happy if this was to be
the second Golden Age.
[URARA]
Hey, everybody!
Good afternoon!
(Laughs)
You ready for the selection?
I am your acting emcee
for this battle.
I'm Urara Kawashima!
Hello! (Giggle)
(Boys cheer wildly)
(Girls growl wildly)
Congratulations to those of
you who were awesome enough
to make the final cut!
If you'll take a quick look at
the signboard, you will see...
the sixty of you who were
chosen are split into groups
of A and B.
Each block will have their
own round of preliminaries,
first A and then B.
The top contestants from
each block will earn the
right to move on
and compete in the
actual tournament event!
(Loud cheers)
Okay, guys...
Now it's time for
a message from Eizan,
who's on this years
action committee:
"The Selection will be
attended by several VIPs
and leading authorities
of the culinary world.
This is an excellent chance
to show off your skills.
"However...
[EIZAN]
...if you present
an inferior dish,
any future plans you
may have had regarding
advancing as a chef
will certainly be crushed.
"So, for the rest of your
summer vacation you better..."
Study hard.
(Confused murmurs)
[URARA]
And that's all!
Ooohh!
We got this thing
in the bag, yo!
I am makin' it to
the final round, man!
[ERINA]
Congratulations on
making the Selection.
But with your skills,
it was only natural.
Ma'am!
I will make sure my performance
won't bring you shame
as your faithful aide.
Also, please rest assured!
It will be a tremendous honor to
get to punish Soma for you!
Uggh...
Ah, I'm so sorry!
I spoke out of turn!
the goal of this
training camp
wasn't just the means
to weed people out.
There's no way you'll be picked
to be a member of the selection.
"Selection"?
There's no way they'll
ever choose you
for something as fine as this!
Don't get cocky,
Soma Yukihira.
Erina Nakiri is by
far your superior.
[SOMA]
I didn't see Erina's
name up there.
Nope.
Council of Ten has
to oversee things.
They're in charge of the
Fall Selection every year.
Erina's too busy.
She's on the administrative end.
Hmm?
Ah! Man!
It's gonna be a while
before I can battle Erina.
Sure enough...
the other members
are super elite.
I really get the feeling I
don't belong!
How come we didn't make
the cut, but somehow that
loser country bumpkin' did?
My cooking skills and class
ranking are both way
higher than that little hick.
It makes no sense!
Total bull crap, man.
Shut your hole!
You mindless dolts!
If you think the selection
is based solely on grades,
then you nut jobs are even
dumber than you look.
Candidates are judged on ALL
aspects, from their character
to future prospects.
AHH!
Anyone who's content just
getting good scores...
has no business
being chosen anyway!
Look at that impression!
(Frightened screams)
U‐um, thank you!
Miss, uh...
I'm Miyoko Hojo.
And you're Megumi Tadokoro.
You've piqued my curiosity.
[MIYOKO]
Chef Kojiro Shinomiya made his
name as a former member of the
Tohtsuki Council of Ten.
Are the rumors true
that you challenged him
to a Food War back at camp?
And did you somehow manage
to pull out a draw?
Uh, uh... No, um,
I swear to you it really
wasn't an even draw at all!
Don't tell me...
that you beat him!
NO!
N‐no, it was‐
Well what it is?!
Spit it out, girl!
It was, uh,
it was all thanks to Soma.
I'm no good on
my own, honestly.
If it wasn't for
Soma, I would be... Uhhh...
Soma Yukihira,
that transfer student?
Oh, I see.
So in the end, you just let
some man do it for you?
Sorry I bothered you.
I thought you
were someone else.
[ALICE]
Let me explain something, Soma.
Most of the current
members of the Council of Ten
have fought in the
Fall Selection's final battle.
It's one of the ways to
get chosen as a member.
In other words,
I'm sure you figured out,
one of us is going to go
on to become the next
member of The Ten.
[NAO]
Aah, Miss Erina.
You're as beautiful as always.
With those eyes...
with your words...
I want you to scorn me as
your unworthy disciple!
RAAGH! That little tramp!
I hate your face!
I'm far more suited to be
with Miss Erina than you!
[MIYAMOTO]
I'm sure the members have
been announced by now.
[MADOKA]
Yes, they have.
Hello, Zenji.
[ALICE]
Of course...
the point is moot
unless one wins here.
I hope the day comes
when you, Erina, and I
can battle it out
for a spot on The Ten.
Hmph.
[JOICHIRO]
There's a stain from a
spilt pot of stew.
I was cooking up
there one night.
Don't go losing to anyone,
till you've lost to me again.
And I look forward
to crushing you.
Time to get down to business...
Come and get some.
Aaah... such a lovely
refreshing morning, isn't it?
Simply perfect for the
first day of summer.
[YUKI]
Hey!
I've got it, it finally came!
It's here!
Look. It's from the
Fall Selection Office.
[SOMA]
Uh! Well, let's open it up!
[TOGETHER]
Curry...
Cuisine?
Hmph!
[SOMA]
So then, are we just supposed to
make any old curry and rice?
Well, it said "cuisine," so...
it doesn't HAVE to be
limited just to that.
'Kay, so, some sort of dish
within the curry family.
Is that really it?
I guess so!
What do you think, Isshiki?
(Laugh)
Well, who can say?
[YUKI] Hey, don't
dodge the question!
[SOMA] Curry...
That covers way
too much ground.
It doesn't even give
us a starting point.
Oh!
This place...
Kyokusei Dormitory...
What was it like
for you living here?
I had a blast.
Everyone brushing up
their cooking skills, in
whatever way they liked...
Yeah, there was one of us
who made nothing but curry.
Hm?
Yep, the kid's
name was Shiomi.
Went on to become a fine
teacher at Tohtsuki.
If you cross paths,
drop my name.
I always had
Shiomi's back.
[JOICHIRO]
Y'oughta get a favor
or two that way.
[SOMA]
So anyway, that's
what my dad told me.
Yeah?
Looks like we're made it.
Huh?!
[SOMA]
It's a lot more
rundown than I expected.
[MEGUMI]
He might be even scarier
than Mr. Chapelle!
Excuse me!
[SOMA]
Shiomi, Shiomi...
Excuse us.
Huh? No one's here?
Whoa! Nevermind!
Huuh?
Hello there...
I have visitors!
Um, I'm sorry! I'll put
some tea on right away!
I'm sorry! I'm really
really sorry for the
state of this place!
She's so tiny. Is she
in school with us?
No, we're the
ones who are sorry.
I'm sorry for being
so inattentive to visitors.
It's our fault for intruding.
No, it's perfectly all right.
Please forgive me!
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
These two are gonna run out
of things to apologize for.
[SOMA]
Um, do you know where the
teacher for this classroom is?
And could you
please tell him that
Joichiro Saiba's son is here.
Whuuuuuu...
Hya! HYA! HYA!
Joichiro Saiba's son?!
Get outta here, right now,
or else I will throw you out!
Huh?! Um, he's
unconscious right now,
so I don't think he
will be moving.
That's too bad!
I didn't need any reminders
of that creep
walking in here to torture me!
Hey, Jun.
I bought all that stuff
you asked for.
Sorry for the bother!
Hey, make sure
you're taking good shots.
Do NOT make me
look chubby.
Get a good angle.
[RYO]
You look good
from every angle.
Yes, yes I know!
Aah...
[JUN]
I look forward to staying
here with you all.
I‐I'm Jun Shiomi.
Hello, and welcome
to Kyokusei Dorm.
I heard that you were able
to clear Miss Fumio's little
entrance exam on your first try.
That's very
promising indeed.
Th‐thank you so very much!
[JOICHIRO]
Mornin'.
[GIN]
Joichiro! C'mon. Why aren't
you in your uniform?
We got a newbie, huh?
Welcome to our
friendly little abode.
Wanna try one of my
new dishes? Would'ya?
Y‐yes! Please by all means!
(Sinister laugh)
[JUN]
And that's how
Joichiro Saiba used me,
the youngest resident at
Kyokusei at the time.
I was his guinea pig.
Utterly tormenting me
with his new dishes
at every opportunity
he could find.
And then, he inflicted
a wound to my heart that
will never be healed.
But you look exactly the same
as you did in that flashback!
Ah, that's because
I've been eating spices
for a very long time.
Many of them help aid
in beauty enhancement.
Really? You mean
that's all it takes?!
My dad did some
pretty cruel things.
His underclassman had it
rough while he was here.
Wouldn'tcha say, Megumi?
(Groan)
[MEGUMI]
Um, well, we're residents
at Kyokusei,
and we thought you could
tell us about curry.
Yes, that's right.
That's the theme of
the Fall Selection is‐
Hmph! I will only talk
to the sweet little girl
sitting over there.
I will have nothing to say
to either Joichiro or any
of his filthy blood relatives.
[AKIRA]
Yeah, I'm really
sorry about that guys.
We finally get some visitors,
and you end up getting
the cold shoulder.
Hi, my name is Akira Hayama...
I'm a freshman here
just like you.
Huh? I didn't think you
could take special seminars
till your second year.
Yeah, well...
The thing is,
she kinda needs me.
You see, messing around with
spices is pretty much the only
thing she really does.
Isn't that right, Jun?
Don't call me Jun!
It's "Professor Shiomi"!
You're my helper, Akira,
so you need to show me some
proper respect around here!
Jun... It's your turn
to water the plants.
You forgot again.
Flinch!
So I watered them for you again.
Okay, I'm sorry.
And you forgot last week too...
and almost killed an important
herb dear to both of us.
Uh, yeah, that was my fault.
Oh and who was it that
entertained the visitors you
stood‐up last month as well? Hm?
You, Akira...
She's getting
even smaller...
[MEGUMI]
Soma, you gotta see this!
[SOMA]
Wow, that's an awesome
collection of spices!
This totally
smells like curry!
[AKIRA]
It's a spice called karipatta.
It is also quite well known
as the "curry leaf."
Huh? You really have
raw curry leaves here?
You know about
this stuff, Megumi?
Yeah.
As seedlings, they can't
handle cold weather
and will wither before
the winter's over.
That's why dried leaves are
the most common here in Japan.
It has to be almost
impossible to find
them raw around here!
Yeah, that's one of the main
focuses for Jun's research:
Finding a way to safely
cultivate spices from tropical
areas here in Japan.
She's found a freezing method
to preserve them for long
periods of time,
and in doing so, she's
come up with several new
flavor components.
Well, you are a lot
more awesome than
you look, Professor!
I don't appreciate
praise from the likes
of someone like YOU...
But you're getting it.
That's just how
much potential
spices can truly
hide within them.
After all, spices are...
Fragrance, heat, color...
They influence all
three of these!
Combining them produces a
synergistic effect.
The more spices included,
the more their qualities
are lessened!
If combined haphazardly,
it becomes muddled.
The limit is approximately
20 varieties.
Fats and oils are essential
for drawing out a
spice's flavors...
Uh‐oh. So we're getting a
full‐blown lecture now.
Also, the fats will taste
their absolute best when they're
in an emulsified state...
When she gets like this,
it could be a while.
[AKIRA]
I think it might be faster if
you just try it for yourselves.
Have a taste.
I'll show you the
true depth of spice.
[AKIRA]
Here's your first dish.
It's a chicken
Kolivartha curry.
It's a signature dish hailing
from southern India.
It uses some of the
curry leaf for fragrance.
Whoa‐ho! This looks
really freakin' good!
What is this?!
First, the strong scent
of the curry leaf
shoots through the nose,
and then right behind that
comes a light, tingling heat
of peppers and onions...
that spreads across the
entire tongue!
[AKIRA]
That intensity
is the raw leaf.
The raw leaves give
off 10 times more fragrance
than any dry ones can.
Okay, now for the next dish.
This is a Goan Fish Curry.
You can use any medium size
white fish, like swordfish.
Huh? Another curry?
[AKIRA]
All the other ingredients and
spices are exactly the same.
But compare the two.
This dish is even more
delicious?! How could it be?
Yes. For that one, I pan‐fried
the red pepper and coriander.
In other words,
I used roasted spices.
That's enough to make
that big of a difference?
That is truly incredible, Akira!
Now I totally understand.
It makes perfect sense.
If your dish is supported
by pan‐roasted spices,
it will blend all
the ingredients' flavors
in perfect harmony!
And finally, there's this.
It looks like the
same Kolivartha curry
we ate the first time.
Yeah. But it's
different though!
The aroma of the
curry leaf is way more
intense than it was before!
Oh... Wow...
The level of heat that
spreads on the tongue
is totally changed!
The level of flavor is even
more pronounced than before!
Correct. And I didn't add
a single ingredient more.
But instead of using
a soup stock...
I just simmered
it in plain water.
In water?!
It's exactly what
Jun said earlier:
Spices need care. If too many
varieties are mixed in...
they will lose their
individual impressions.
This would be the opposite.
By deliberately removing the
flavor of the stock,
it creates a curry where
the spices' impact is
drastically heightened.
Normally, you'd think
that would certainly weaken
the flavor of a dish...
But instead, there's no
denying the remarkable levels
of fragrance this has reached!
I've been pierced!
To think, slightly changing
the way spices are used
could change a dish
so dramatically!
This guy...
The whole time
he was cooking...
he didn't look inside
the pot even once.
The fennel has started
to smell fragrant.
It will be done cooking
in about five minutes.
It'll be another 40 seconds
for the coconut paste.
Then it blends.
[SOMA]
He could tell the state of the
dish just by the scent of the
spices and ingredients alone!
That's impressive.
So what can I tell you?
It's in this way Jun
needs my help.
Hello? Where did everyone go?
I take the theories
she comes up with
and refine them
into actual dishes.
You see, that is the
role I play here.
[MEGUMI]
A theoretical scientist
and a hands‐on chef!
Honestly, it gave me
good chuckle when
I heard the theme
of the Selection's
preliminaries.
"Curry cuisine,"
of all things.
So you're in this year's
Fall Selection, too?
I will be in A‐Block with you,
Soma Yukihira.
Wait. Did I tell
you my name?
Oh, come on, everyone
knows who you are
at this academy!
Well, everyone who attended
opening ceremonies, that is.
Look, your cooking
is interesting.
Even with your options
limited, you've come up
with a way to pull through.
But still, that's not
enough for you to "take
the top spot" at Tohtsuki.
Well before you can taste it,
even before you can see it,
the first thing that
reaches the senses...
And that which lingers
when the food is chewed,
and swallowed away...
Is the essence of FRAGRANCE.
It's the key to
masterful cuisine.
Only one can be at the top.
And that's going to be me.
Well thank you
for the lesson.
Your curry dishes
were truly incredible.
I'll look forward
to next time.
"Next time"?
When we're up there on
that Selection stage,
I'll treat you to a curry
that's even better.
AH!
Are you serious?
You think I would
lose to YOUR curry?
Soma, did you learn
nothing while eating
what I made for you?
Course I did,
and I got scared, too.
Huh?
I said "here's someone
who can make something
I can't even fathom."
At least not yet.
And I admit it makes
me kinda jealous.
But it really taught
me a lot about curry.
See you again at
the preliminaries‐ URGH!
I was in the middle
of my lecture!
The doorknob... it
got me in the stomach.
Ah! Please!
I'm so very sorry!
Soma Yukihira...
Ugghh?
[AKIRA]
Taking on curry means
taking on spices
and living in a world dominated
by scents and fragrances...
And my nose is something
very special.
You don't stand a chance
of defeating me, my friend.
[JUN]
Ah, I'm sorry!
I was spacing out!
Next time, it's Food Wars'
twentieth course:
"Dragon Lies Prone
then Ascends to the Sky"
Sorry! What should
I say next? Um, um, um...
Summer vacation!
Summer vacation.
Summer vacation...