(Restaurant chatter)
Buon appetito.
You've sure come
a long way, Takumi.
And with Isami here, Aldini's
future is in very good hands.
Takumi... You wanna go
out on a date?
You're as cute as always,
Takumi.
Why don't you play
with an older girl?
Oh honey.
We need to go somewhere and
make each other feel good...
Mwah.
Si, grazie.
I do appreciate all
the sentiments,
but there is something
that I must do.
[UNCLE]
So uh... are you really okay
with letting them both go,
brother?
[FATHER]
I am.
Now, I may be a bit biased,
but they have both
grown into excellent chefs.
But Takumi seems...
to have grown a cold
place in his heart.
You're sending us
to cooking school?!
Uncle, this really
doesn't make any sense.
Why would we need
to go there?
We have been proving ourselves
at Aldini for eight years now.
[UNCLE]
Well. You would
benefit greatly by going.
That school is respected
the world over.
Just leave everything
to my brother...
Your father will make all
your travel arrangements.
Come back once you've managed
to sharpen your skills.
Transferring into the second
year of culinary school...
What do you
think about this?
I'll just go wherever
you go, brother.
[FATHER]
After a few more years, Takumi
may very well surpass me...
but he can't see the goal
that lies ahead of him.
What he needs is to face
a competitive rival.
There's no way I can lose
to a chef my own age.
I've already fought so hard in
the kitchens.
I'm a professional chef.
[SOMA]
Now sure, my transfer
was kinda unexpected,
but I still don't plan on
losing to a bunch of wannabes
who've never stood in front
of a customer before.
I mean, come on, am I right?
Anyway, since I'm here
and everything.
I might as well take
the top spot.
HM!
(Opening Song)
Mezzaluna!
Tritare!
Okay!
[TAKUMI]
Tre...
Due...
Uno...
[BOTH in Italian]
Fine!
[HINAKO]
This salsa verde duck
was infused with Japanese
elements in a measured and
creative way.
A flawless combination
of Japanese technique
and imagination.
Takumi Aldini, Isami Aldini,
you both pass!
Grazie!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
That was way too fast!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
And they still had time
to dress the duck!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
That didn't even take an hour!
Well then, Soma Yukihira.
It would seem you haven't made
much progress yet.
You have a long way
to go to measure up.
Oh yes, right.
You had mentioned a
challenge earlier, didn't you?
Very well.
If I'm to expect a dish
as scrumptious as the
previous one,
I will gladly make an exception,
and weigh in on which is better.
Did you hear
that, Soma?!
Yeah! You're not
gonna hear me object!
The loser will be
forced to grovel.
You'll grovel in front
of your opponent and say
"I'm a loser and a dog!"
three times for all to hear.
If you're putting your
restaurants' reputations
on the line,
we need something
of this magnitude.
[BOTH] Uhh...
Ah! But my sweet
little dumpling,
YOU won't have to grovel,
only the silly boys will.
You have some
lovely fingers.
She is seriously
creeping me out!
Let's go!
You think you can make
something better?
Give it your best shot!
These guys came up with
the idea to use duck
completely on the fly...
Plus, they gathered a
range of ingredients
to complement its flavor.
Makes me wonder...
What's the best dish I could
make in a situation like this?
[HINAKO]
Use the ingredients here to
make a dish emphasizing
traditional Japanese cooking.
There were a few chickens and
rabbits out there, too.
Hehehe.
Megumi!
Yes?!
I wanna use these
ingredients as garnish.
Could ya get 'em for me?
You know what
these are, right?
I think so...
Yes, don't worry
about a thing.
I used to forage for a
lot of greens back home.
Great! I am counting on you!
What're you gonna
be doing, Soma?
There's something I'm
gonna need to find.
I'm headed outside.
Oh! But first...
Chef Hinako?
I can use absolutely
anything
within the fenced
boundaries correct?
Yes. Well.
As long as it's within
the permitted area,
use what you like.
Perfect.
In that case a key
ingredient in what
we are gonna
prepare for you is...
Heh!
is this!
Ah!
Wha...
Uh... But that's my snack!
I was just
eating that!
Huh? Rice crackers?!
Looks like we'll be going
back outside again.
Oh. Could you hold
these for me? Thanks.
Uh? What makes you
think I‐ Eck!
[SOMA]
All right! Let's go, Megumi!
O‐okay!
So what am I
supposed to eat now?
Soma Yukihira...
Just what are you planning?
Um! Huh!
Okay. I've gotten
everything on my end.
(Clucking)
Ow! Grr!
If these chickens are out
in force, then...
There!
These are MINE!
Perfectly warm,
freshly laid eggs!
(Hinako sighs)
This doesn't taste good.
Make it again.
(Collective sigh)
[ALL]
We're so not gonna pass this!
We have worked so hard on
this dish but only a few
teams have passed so far.
I don't think we have a chance.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Hinako Inui...
Member of Tohtsuki Academy's
80th graduating class.
When she was still a
student, they called her the
"Empress of the Mist."
She was a fearsome chef.
The Empress of the Mist?!
Don't understand it,
but it sounds cool.
Why do they call her
something like that?
I guess this is all
that I can expect.
It's been an endless stream
of dish after dish of broiled
fish with the same texture.
I'd like to eat something
a bit more substantial.
[SCHOOLBOY]
That's easy for her to say.
We're stuck out here in the
middle of freakin' nowhere!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
Just what is she trying
to tell us to make?!
Oh! You can redo your dishes
as many times as you like
until the time runs out.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
AHH! We need to make it again!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Are you nuts?
There's not enough time!
It's a good thing we decided
to use duck for our dish, huh?
Soma isn't back yet.
That idiot's going to
run out of time.
You need to stop
worrying about him.
If he doesn't make it,
you'll win by default,
so it all works out.
What I want is to have
an epic cooking battle!
I don't want to
win by some default!
Okay...
Why would he want me
to hold onto this?
How is he going to use
it in his dish?
(Panting)
Huh? There you are!
Yeah? What?
Hey! You only have 15
minutes left, dumbass!
Are you trying to lose
and get kicked out
right off the freakin' bat?!
You're crushing their
rice crackers, man.
Hm?
Ah! I'm sorry! I
wasn't trying to ruin
your your ingredients!
I promise, man!
Yeah, don't worry about it.
You saved me some work.
Thank you.
Also, 15 minutes
is plenty of time.
What the...?
If a restaurant
keeps customers waiting,
then they pick up
and go somewhere else.
Here we go, Megumi!
Yeah!
I saved him some work?
Hehe.
I need to prep
these wild greens.
First, I'll need to
slice the bottom ends
off the pepper buds.
Careful... Careful...
When you're done with that,
could you separate the yolks
from the whites?
'Kay!
Huh?! A fried dish?
Yup, we'll fry
the fish we caught.
Yeah okay,
I guess...
but we don't have any
flour or cornstarch...
Nothing to act
as a breading.
How do you plan
on deep‐frying it?
The fish has a lot of moisture,
so without any breading it's
not going to fry up properly.
Actually, we do have some.
We've got an excellent
breading!
Uh...
Freshwater fish...
Eggs...
Rice crackers...
Ah! I've got it!
Soma is going to take
the rice crackers...
and crush them to
use as a breading!
All right! We're done!
Chef Hinako...
Please have some
before it gets cold.
Great. This looks good.
Oh! My rice crackers were used
to make an excellent fried dish!
(Gasps)
Now this has such
a wonderful texture!
It's so crispy.
And the fish is nice and warm!
The coating protected the char,
concentrating its flavor.
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[HINAKO]
The flavor of the
rice crackers themselves
gives the coating
another layer of complexity.
And on the side, we have a
light and fluffy sauce using
eggs and pepper buds.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
He used eggs as a base?
And it looks like he added
salad oil to the yolks.
And then whisked it up.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Oh yeah. So that's his sauce?
Then he added to the eggs,
salt and shaved pepper buds,
the young sansho leaves.
That gave it a
refreshing sensation,
tempering the oil and
creating a refined flavor.
The creaminess of the sauce
glistening between bites
of the crispy coating
really rouses the appetite.
The treatment of the fried
vegetables was skillful as
well.
providing a vibrant
counterpoint to the char.
(Giggle)
I've assigned this challenge
several times,
and while deep‐frying
is one thing,
I've never had a student give
me a breaded dish.
(Blowing)
(Crunch echoes)
And it works.
The rice crackers bound with
a seasonal freshwater fish.
It's like a warm embrace
with a majestic mermaid,
brimming with fiery emotion.
[MERMAID]
Ohh!
(Aquatic whimpers)
Yes!
Oooh!
OOOHHH!
I'm going to drown...
in crispy
rice‐crackery love!
MMmm!
Soma, how did you come up
with something like this?
We have okaki‐age that's
used in Japanese cooking, right.
We pound down the rice crackers,
then use it as a coating
to fry the ingredients,
giving the dish an unexpected
texture and flavor.
I've made it back home
and it always satisfies.
So you came up with
the idea to use kaki no
tane in the same way.
It's called:
"Yukihira‐style okaki‐age..."
Oh! Or now I guess:
"Yukihira‐style
O‐kaki no Tane‐age Char!"
You just thought of that
right now, didn't you?!
Mm...
Had it all planned out!
You're making crap up
as you go along!
[SOMA]
Everything went
according to plan.
[HINAKO]
Aldini has a broad
perspective on things.
(Arguing continues)
He didn't overlook duck
as a possible ingredient.
On the other hand, Soma was
exceptionally creative.
He made something no one
else here even considered
as an option.
Even with time and
conditional constraints,
he set out to cook his own
dish his own way.
That resolve is the mark
of a professional chef.
Soma Yukihira,
Megumi Tadokoro,
you have passed!
You're welcome, Ma'am!
Hmph!
[SOMA]
Um, a Spaghetti
Napolitan?
[TAKUMI]
No!
Okay, class, that's enough.
Today's cooking
challenge is over.
(Sighs of relief)
Thank goodness!
[SCHOOLGIRL] (Crying)
No! Not yet!
I'm screwed...
[TAKUMI]
Chef Hinako...
Huh?
Are you going to tell us
who won the battle?
Uh...
Very well.
The winner is...
[HINAKO]
The one with an idea that
no one thought of,
BY creating a perfectly
textured char...
HM?!
Uh...
No, no, wait. Please
give me a minute.
HUH?!
Okay, I've decided!
The person who didn't
overlook the opportunity
to use duck in his dish...
and took great care in his work.
(Gasp)
Wait, maybe I need to
think on it some more.
GUUHH!
(Laugh)
What is this lady doing?
She's weird?
(Ringing)
Uh, what?
Oh, who wants me?
I'm in the middle
of a very important‐
[KOJIRO]
What are you doing,
Hinako?!
OH!
Is there a problem?
Your group should've
been back a long time ago!
You need to hurry up
and get over here,
this is absolutely ridiculous!
Oh! I‐I'm so sorry,
Kojiro!
This class is dismissed!
Everyone needs to hurry
back to the hotel, okay?!
Huh?!
What about
your judgment?
Gah!
Oh, that's right.
My final say is...
I'll take it under
consideration!
[HINAKO]
Okay, back to the bus ASAP!
Uuhh...
How can she do
that to us?!
She ran off before
giving a verdict!
This is not even close
to being over!
Mark my words:
Soma, one day we WILL
settle who is the best chef!
Yeah, maybe, but how do
you plan to get the‐
In a Food War.
One day, I'll submit
my challenge.
And you will
accept your fate.
[TAKUMI]
When that time comes...
I will pound you.
Until then, you should hone your
skills to the utmost perfection.
Next time I see you,
it is on!
[HINAKO]
Those in back go ahead and
move up. Okay, off we go!
(Awkward grunts)
Well, whattya know...
Should we do it now?
Shut up! Don't talk to me!
(Stifling laughter)
[SOMA]
Come on! I'm right here!
Do it, already!
[TAKUMI]
I said not to talk to me!
I used my skills and my
knowledge to the fullest
in today's challenge.
When the inspiration
for that dish hit me,
I was sure that I'd win.
For him to be in the
same league with me...
Dammit! There was no clear
judgment,
so why do I feel
like I've lost?
I cannot let things
end like this.
One day I WILL beat you,
Soma Yukihira!
[SOMA]
Takumi from
Trattoria Aldini...
So there's someone the same age
as me whose come this far.
If I'd just stayed at Yukihira,
I never would've known.
[YUKI]
Megumi! Soma!
You made it!
(Vibrant laugh)
[MEGUMI]
Hi, Yuuki. Hi, Ryoko. Heard
anything about the others?
Shun is over there trying
to find out right now.
[SHUN]
Understood. Thank you.
Looks like we all
made it through.
Everyone from Kyokusei survived.
Thank goodness!
So, uh...
(Zenji groaning)
am I right to say
that Zenji made it?
Apparently he was running around
like a mad man in the mountains.
Nice!
Our group had a
similar challenge.
Gosh, that was
unbelievably exhausting.
I'm so tired,
I can barely move!
Whatever are you saying,
my young ladies?
[BOTH]
Hm?
It's time for us
to enjoy our reward!
What reward?
Huh?
[YUKI]
Dinner...
a hot bath...
and our fancy rooms!
I'm sure they'll be luxurious,
utterly gorgeous and comfy!
And you know, I will enjoy them
like it's the last day on earth!
[BOTH]
FLEX, BABY!
Uh!
[SEKIMORI]
You'll have some free
time once you're done
making dinner for
these gentlemen.
Who the heck are all
these muscle heads?!
They're members of the Upper Arm
University's Bodybuilding Club,
which is holding a
training camp down the road.
[SEKIMORI]
The football and wrestling
clubs will also be joining us.
FLEX!
[SEKIMORI]
Tonight's meal will
be a steak dinner.
You'll need to make 50 servings
each for this challenge.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Fifty servings each?!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
WHAT?! Starting right now?!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
That's friggin'
ridiculous!
Chef Sekimori,
what about OUR dinner?
Once you've made
fifty plates,
you are allowed to go ahead
and cook your own dinner.
Wait what? We have to do what?
I thought someone
would cook for us.
That's not going to happen.
AHHHH!
[SEKIMORI]
While you're here,
you'll be in charge of
making your own meals.
That would be breakfast,
lunch, and dinner.
Please keep that in mind.
[RYOKO]
Ah! I can hear the sound
of Yuki's soul dying inside.
[SEKIMORI]
Oh, one more thing:
Anyone who is unable to complete
their dishes in an hour,
will be summarily expelled
from the academy.
(Shocked gasps and screams)
Good luck.
HAH?!
(Screaming)
(Dishes clattering)
Hey, you are NOT
cutting ahead of me!
Well you're just
standing there!
This, this, and this:
It's not enough.
Make it again.
U‐uhhh...
[ATHLETES]
More! MORE!
Where's the food at?!
Bring me ten more bowls!
I can't raise my arms!
We still have
30 dishes left...
I can't take it!
It won't end.
It just won't end!
Hey, Zenji, you okay?
(Fluttered breaths)
This training camp
really is pure evil.
(Hissing and snarling)
Feed us!
They are demons sent
from hell!
[SEKIMORI]
Soma Yukihira, you've
completed fifty servings.
You pass.
You're welcome!
That was fast!
(Isami humming)
Crap! I fell behind!
Soma Yukihira! Mine will taste
better than yours! Probably!
You! Use your hands
instead of your mouth!
Yes, sir.
Later! I'll be
in Zenji's room.
But I was thinking of going
to bed early tonight, you
dumb butt‐munch!
Get a move on, dork!
Yahh! Yes sir!
He still wants to
hang out tonight?
(Ending Song Begins)
That Soma...
He's one tough cookie!
I told everyone that I'd
be in Zenji's room...
but if I'm the first one
to get there...
There're won't be
anything for me to do.
Hm?
A public bath?
Aw yeah! If I'm the
only one who's ready,
then I'll probably have the
whole place to myself right now!
♪I'm gonna go grab me
a robe and some undies!♪
HAHAHAHA!
(Erina hum to ending song)
(Humming continues)
(Soma grunts to ending song)
Ahh...
(Grunting and singing overlap)
[ERINA and SOMA] UH!
Oh, sorry!
Huh?
(Light moan)
(Gasp)
Uggh...
Hmm...
Hm.
[HINAKO]
Next time on Food Wars,
this will be the 10th course!
"The Supreme Recette"
It's quite delicious!
Wouldn't you agree?
[ERINA]
Now, THAT is spice...