(Jiggle jiggle)
(SIGH) I need something
that inspires.
(Lion roar)
No, that's not it.
(Ricocheting bullet)
Still not quite there yet.
I need something
special today.
Ooh! Now we're talking!
(Flames roaring)
(Opening Song)
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
So did you hear about
today's Food War?
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Yeah. It's Meat‐Meat
vs. Bowl‐club, right?
Man, you gotta feel
sorry for Bowl‐club.
I mean, Erina Nakiri
has it out for them.
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
Yo, have you read
the Tohtsuki Sports?!
It says someone else
is cooking.
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
Look! Now it's that uppity
transfer student,
Soma Yukihira!
[KANICHI]
Here are the tools and
ingredients you'll need
for the battle.
I got everything
you asked for.
Nice.
Thanks again for
all your help!
So were you able to get
any sleep last night?
Uh...
Well when we were done,
I wanted tweaked the sauce
a little bit more.
I slept about two hours,
I guess.
Uh...
(Distant crowd chatter)
So many people!
Soma! Whatever you do don't
look out in the audience!
You don't want to
lose your nerve!
Alright, there's
no need to freak out,
everything is going
to be just fine, okay?
Just be calm and
don't lose it!
Yeah, yeah...
First, you need to calm
yourself down, m'kay?
Huh?!
You're not even a
little bit scared?
[MEGUMI]
I mean you have to cook
with all those people watching.
[SOMA]
Not at all.
Huh?
I mean,
Not compared to standing
in front of customers
with my family restaurant's
name on the line.
If I do end up
beating you...
would that make me
the new Tohtsuki No. 7?
[URARA]
Sorry for the wait, you guys!
The Food War Administrative
Bureau has officially recognized
this challenge as a Food War!
(Crowd cheers)
And as always,
I will be your emcee.
I'm Urara Kawashima,
a freshman in the
high school division!
Love you!
You're cutest
thing ever, Urara!
HEY!
WE LOVE YOU!
[URARA]
Now then, from their
respective corners,
here come the contestants!
(Cheers)
[URARA]
The first contestant
to join the battle...
The Meat Master, Ikumi Mito!
(Laughs)
(Cheers)
Oh, don't go flaunting
those big udders of yours,
you little hussy!
I am all the boys in this
school will ever need!
I am the cutest thing
to ever walk this earth!
And now! To introduce our
next contestant...
Eat crap, you
dirty transfer!
Who do you
think you are?!
Go back home
to your diner!
This is the part where you
get what's coming to ya, a‐hole!
The transfer student who's
been garnering rave reviews
here at the academy,,
Soma Yukihira!
[ONLOOKER 1]
If he's facin' Mito, I already
know who's winning this one.
He's toast. There's no way
I'm gonna miss seeing him get
expelled from this Academy.
(Nervous whimpers)
What is with all
these rude people
and their attitudes?
I'll never forget.
Back when I battled the
Standing‐While‐Eating‐Soba
Research Society,
there was no emcee,
not even an audience!
The only ones there
were stray dogs drawn
by the scent of food.
(Loud booing)
[KANICHI]
What is their problem?
Soma, didn't you just
transfer here this spring?
Why do they all
hate you so much?
Dunno.... I haven't done
anything that I know of.
(Whimpers)
[URARA]
Let's have a quick review
of the rules, shall we?
We have three
honorary judges.
The theme is "rice bowls."
And the main ingredient
for today's battle is...
meat!
(Cheers)
[URARA]
If Ikumi Mito wins,
the Rice Bowl Research
Society will be disbanded,
and Soma Yukihira
will leave the Academy.
But if Soma wins,
the "Bowl‐club" will
get more funding
and additional cooking
facilities.
Also...
Ikumi will become
a member of Bowl‐club!
(Astonished murmurs)
Hey there, short‐timer.
It looks like this will be
your last day here.
If you have any last words,
now's the time.
You think so?
(Swish)
I think we'll have plenty of
time to talk
once you're a member
of Bowl‐club.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Look, over there!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Dude! Erina Nakiri!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
O.M.G! It's her!
[IKUMI]
Erina...
[YUKI]
Whoa, for real?
Why's she here?
Why would a member of
the Ten show up for this?
Especially to see something
as lame as the Bowl‐club?
Probably because she's part
of Erina's faction.
You really think that's it?
Or is there some other reason?
Well, Soma Yukihira,
I am so looking
forward to this.
I cannot wait to see you
suffer a humiliating defeat.
[IKUMI]
Why would Miss Erina come
to watch this in person?
Contestants, are you ready?!
Get to your cooking stations!
[URARA]
It is winner take all...
in this battle
decided by the palate!
Let the Food War...
BEGIN!
(Horn blows)
[IKUMI]
Hey, transfer student.
Let me show you the kind
of ingredient a pissant like you
will never get to use.
Hm?
Presenting...
the ultimate grade of beef!
Man, I knew she'd
bring that sucker out.
That is some
A5‐ranked beef!
(Whimper)
Yah! HAH! AGH!
(Grunting)
That is one massive
butcher cleaver.
She's making precision cuts
even with that huge blade!
Aaaugh! She can really
cut some meat!
[AOKI]
Dude! Will you
look at that slab?!
I've never seen marbling
as fine as that!
[SATO]
Man! Both the
meat and the fat
have some sweet luster!
(Pleasant sigh)
(Sniff)
Good girl...
Your subtle sweetness
tickles the senses...
As meat is smoked,
flavor components like glutamic
acid are increased,
and it starts to emit
a gentle, sweet aroma.
This is the ultimate meat,
and it will be cooked by the
ultimate hands: mine.
Mmm...
[IKUMI]
First, fry it to give the
surface some color.
Scoop up the butter
and pour it all over the
meat's glistening surface.
(Laughs)
The aroma of melted butter
is wafting throughout
the whole building!
Ahh! It's making me ravenous
from just the scent alone.
(Astonished gasps)
So rad!
(Chuckle)
This process creates
a "barrier"
that traps the meat's
savory juices inside.
Next...
It goes into the oven!
This will apply heat to the
meat's interior.
Now then...
What about the
transfer student?
[URARA]
Meanwhile, as for
Soma's dish...
It seems he sure is dicing
up an awful lot of onion.
Just how do you think he plans
on using them all? Wha‐?!
[URARA]
It looks like he's
bringing out the meat!
So, how will it stack up
to the A5 beef?
Huh?!
(Mutters and groans)
It was on sale?
Uh... Half‐price?!
Huh?
Hehe. I got it out
of the bargain bin.
Musta been my lucky day.
(Awkward laugh)
You are a disgrace!
Unbelievable!
Oh my god! Stop it!
What in the heck are
you ingrates doing?!
Do you really think Soma
is going to be able
to make it through
all this?
(Laughs)
Why don't you just
give up already?
Use the time you have left to
go pack your things.
(Oven opening)
Hm.
[ERINA]
Do you know what it is...
that makes her different?
Aside from the cut itself,
it's the way she treats it.
[ERINA]
That is correct.
But her true worth
is her delicate touch,
She knows exactly
what the meat needs.
There's no one more sensitive.
64 degrees...
No, it's more like 65.
Perfect.
[ERINA]
And Ikumi Mito
knows that the lips
are the most sensitive
part of the human body.
That being said, when it
comes to distinguishing the
appropriate temperature,
she's on another level.
[ERINA]
And when she
touches the meat,
her prowess becomes
even more evident.
She's something
else...
Watch closely.
See how her fingertips
caress the grains with
loving intention.
Like a pianist playing
an elegant solo.
A silent melody for the heavens.
A carnivorous sonata of meat.
I WILL give Miss Erina
a victory!
[IKUMI]
What, you're still here?
Oh transfer student, you
seem to've gotten pretty
quiet over there, haven't you?
What happened to that attitude
of yours from three days ago?
Hm?
Pah!
Guess it's hard
to talk smack
when you're in a panic.
How pitiful.
[SOMA]
I don't need
to say a thing.
Hm?
'Cause in a bit,
my rice bowl is going to
do all the talking for me.
Huh?
And eloquently, too.
Also, it's common knowledge
that you can't trust a chef
who spends more time
hurling insults than
perfecting their dishes.
(Angry grunt)
You have no idea who
you're dealing with!
(Sizzling)
(Sizzling moans)
Just what is he...
[URARA]
Okay, time's almost up!
(Dramatic music)
(DING)
[URARA]
And we're done!
My favorite books
are fairy tales.
And I love
romance movies, too.
My dream for the future
is to be someone's bride!
I'm so cutesy!
[URARA]
We will now begin judgment.
First up, Ikumi Mito's dish.
[IKUMI]
This is an A5 Wagyu
rôti rice bowl.
[URARA]
Rôti is French for
"roast" or "broil."
So basically, it's like, used
to say food that's been
cooked in an oven, duh!
I love you! Hehe!
The meat has been cut so that
it resembles a flower in bloom.
I never dreamed I'd set eyes on
a rice bowl of such beauty.
I guess it's time to dig in.
This looks really wonderful.
(Squeals of deliciousness)
It's almost too delicious!
I'm getting weak
in the knees!
Amazing! This profound depth of
flavor is truly A5‐grade.
When she was
preparing this meat,
even the angle of heat was
taken into consideration.
When the flame is applied
at a right angle to the
fiber direction,
it causes the meat to heat
uniformly and allows the
juices to run freely.
Taking the meat's fiber
into account is the mark
of a true master chef!
And underneath these "petals"...
This garlic rice was cooked in
melted butter and beef fat.
I would happily eat three bowls
of this exquisite rice alone!
[KATSUNORI]
The way this dish was made,
you could even call it
sensuous!
The execution is simply
incredible!
(Crowd gasps)
What do you think,
transfer student?
This is the pleasure
of the flesh!
Mmm...
That should just
about do it.
I can't wait to see the
look on that transfer's
stupid face when he loses.
This doesn't look
too good.
Everybody out there is acting
like Mito has already won!
[URARA]
Next, We have Soma's dish to
be presented to the judges.
So tell us, what do you
call your rice bowl?
Uh, well...
Let's see, how about,
"Yukihira‐Style Chaliapin
Steak Rice Bowl."
Hm...
You want us to try your
"Chaliapin Steak"?
So all you did was use onions
to make cheap meat tender, huh?
After what we've just eaten...
Hahaha!
Think I'd rather go
home still basking
in the juicy glow
of that A5 meat flower.
Hm?!
(Gulp)
[YOSHIKI]
Uh, well, it does look more
enticing than I'd imagined.
[KATSUNORI]
Uh, shall we have some then?
Tch. He could never use
such cheap meat to make
anything worth a damn.
Ah!
(Ravenous chomping)
What is going on here?!
I can't! My hand
won't stop moving!
Mm! The meat is SO
tender, but also...
The sauce!
This special sauce is
infused with minced onions
and really
whets the appetite!
What is this?!
Such a depth of flavor...
After the steak was cooked,
the frying pan was
deglazed with red wine! OGH!
He simmered the remaining
meat juices in the wine,
and then he used THAT
to fry the onions!
He added cornstarch
to make it smooth
and he allowed it to melt
perfectly with the meat and rice
in a beautiful dance.
The flavors are rounded out
by a mirin‐infused soy sauce!
The browning of the rice gives
it a broad depth of flavor!
Ohh!
Yes!
Yeah, Soma!
Onions are essential to
a Chaliapin Steak,
but it looks like he tweaked it.
And I think he also did
something with the sauce.
So is that really
all there is to it?
But sauce is just... sauce!
It should be no match for
my top‐quality meat!
The meat and the sauce
are both full of flavor
but the more I eat,
the hungrier I get!
You are not kidding.
I feel like I could
eat this forever!
These undertones
of acidity...
Don't tell me...
That's right!
The key to my dish
lies in the rice.
It's the rice?!
The rice in that steak bowl
was mixed with homemade
pickled plum paste.
It's a refreshing
pickled plum rice!
I knew it!
That is the refreshing
taste that makes you
want to keep eating!
The steak is light and fluffy,
and full of deliciousness.
That beautiful sauce
is simply glorious!
And the pickled plum in the
rice is so light and brisk!
Hahaha!
[ALL THREE]
The tastiness of
each component...
elevates the other in harmony!
Uh!
We can't help but scarf it down!
Shredded plums?
That's all it took?
He may have tweaked
things a bit,
but his ingredients
were all cheap!
It doesn't make any sense.
Oh, God!
I'm already finished
with my bowl!
Is there any more left?
Where can we get some
more of this?
[SHIGENO]
The rôti rice bowl
was excellent,
but my chopsticks wanted to
move more towards THIS bowl.
Wait, what was that?!
What about my garlic rice?
They didn't finish it!
[SOMA]
Yup...
I thought long and hard
about how I should
best flavor the
rice in this dish...
[SOMA]
After I heard from Kanichi
that you'd probably use
marbled beef...
I figured you would understand
that you couldn't use any bold
seasonings in the rice,
or else it would clash
with the beef's flavor.
Your dish may look like
a rice bowl, but it's not.
(Gasp)
Like the head of Bowl‐club said:
Cheap and tasty. Meals should
be summarized in one bowl.
Oh just be quiet!
This argument is a
complete waste of time.
With my top‐quality
meat, there's no way
you could've possibly‐
Why don't you give it
a little listen?
Hear what my rice bowl
has to say.
Or are you scared?
(Gasp)
Ooh...
He's right.
This rice bowl
does speak to you.
It says, "Eat me as
fast as you can!"
[IKUMI'S MOM]
Happy ninth birthday, Ikumi!
Thank you so much, Mommy!
I really love it!
(Laughs)
(Tearing)
[IKUMI] Hah?!
[DAD] Put that down!
[MOM]
No. Please don't do this! No!
[DAD]
Shut up! The successor
to the Mito family has
no need for such pleasures!
Listen closely, Ikumi:
Your sole focus
should be on getting
stronger and better!
Understand?!
(Scarfing)
Dammit! Why'd I suddenly
remember something like THAT?
Ah?
It's... It's because of this.
It's whispering to me,
saying it's okay
to do what I want.
That it's okay to be myself!
Dammit...
Ah. Ahh...
Dammit!
(Caramelized moans)
[URARA]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the winner is Soma Yukihira!
(Crowd cheers)
You're welcome!
Incredible, Soma!
[AOKI]
He friggin' did it!
[RYOKO] Yeah!
Way to go!
What?!
I don't believe it...
I lost the Food War.
Ah!
Miss Erina!
[ERINA]
Clear out the
cooking room I gave her.
I have no time
for failures.
Understood, Miss Erina.
[SOMA]
Yo, Meat‐Meat!
Why don't you lemme eat a
little more of your rice bowl?
Don't you talk me,
you dirty little troll!
And stop calling me
Meat‐Meat, you hear me?!
Why not?
You,re probably the best
meat cook I've ever met.
Wh‐what?!
Look forward to
working with you...
Okay, Sweet Meat?
What did you just say?
You piece of crap!
Be sure to come
by the clubroom.
[KANICHI]
Hey, Soma...
Huh?
[KANICHI]
You really are
one hell of a guy.
You're the only one that can
properly keep Bowl‐club afloat.
You're the next
Don of Bowl‐club!
Please, Soma!
(Laughs and cheers)
(Ending Song)
(Annoyed grunts)
[SOMA]
Oh, Sweet Meat.
Brbrbrbrbr!
'Kay. Right.
[IKUMI]
I‐I'm coming in.
Oh, Meat‐Meat, you came!
Of course I did.
So Soma hasn't bothered to
come to class yet, has he?
He told me to come by,
so I felt I didn't really have
much choice in the matter.
[KANICHI]
Um, about that...
Huh?
Nah, I'm not gonna
join your club.
(Both scream)
I mean, all I really wanted
to do was just check it out.
And because I did,
I've built up a great
new menu of rice bowls
that I can try at
the restaurant one day.
Thanks for helping
with everything.
I'll make sure to stop by
once in a while!
So, that's that.
[KANICHI]
Still, we have
more funds now,
so let's work together
to revive Bowl‐club!
You are the only
one that can do it.
Keep us afloat.
You're the next
Don of Bowl‐club!
Meat‐Meat.
Grrrr!
[IKUMI]
Shut the hell up!
Don't call me "Meat‐Meat"! Ahhh!
(Kanichi screams in pain)
[MEGUMI]
Ever since that day,
Ikumi Mito seems to have
grown even more violent...
[MEAT‐MEAT]
RAAAGGHH!
[URARA]
Next time on Food Wars,
it's, like, the eighth course!
"A Concerto of Concept
and Creation"
[AOKI]
That looks delish!
[URARA]
So cutesy!
[KANICHI]
I'm burnt out...
Like coals
turned white.