[CHAPELLE]
So, it is zat time of year
once again, is it? Hm...
What can you tell me about
ze message to ze students?
[TEACHER 1]
It'll be finished today.
Hmm...
Some will prove
zey are worthy...
and others are
destined to fail...
Zis is where
ze culling begins.
(Opening Song)
[SOMA]
Huh?
"Overnight training"?
So it's that
time, is it?
So what is this?
[RYOKO]
We had those in elementary
and middle school.
It was an outing where we
stayed outside for a few days.
[SOMA]
Okay...
So this is one of those
wilderness adventure
schools or whatever.
Eh?
What's wrong
with you, Megumi?
Because she knows...
this training camp
is like a trip to hell.
And we all have to face it
to survive.
Hm...
All of the freshmen
students
get sent to
the mountains
and are subjected
to a whole bunch
of brutal tests.
If you don't manage
to pass everything...
you'll be told to
leave the Academy!
[YUKI]
They say it's for
"the spirit of friendship,"
but the truth of it is...
This training is for the spirit
of pain and torture and failure!
It's not that bad. Just a
little "Competitive education".
[ISSHIKI]
In the words
of the principal,
this is when the process reveals
the best of the best among us.
Yo, bro, didn't you
go to that training
camp last year?
How'd you survive?
Very carefully.
Even back then,
dozens of students were forced
to leave the premises,
and a few others
were even expelled.
What? Expelled?!
At the camp a few years ago...
they apparently got rid of more
than half the students.
(Fainting squeal)
Uh! Megumi?!
Everyone... It's been
nice knowing ya.
Guh!
MEGUMI!
Um, okay. So we're
allowed to bring our
cards or even shogi.
But not our cellphones.
Wait a second here.
This isn't enough time
for us to bathe! C'mon!
Hey, Soma!
How can you be worried
about your bath schedule
at a time like this?!
Did you not just here Megumi
say her dying words?!
Half the students will
make it through, right?
We'll just make sure
that includes all of us.
Uh!
Uh...
[ISSHIKI]
I have faith in all of you.
I'm sure everyone at Kyokusei
will return with grand smiles.
Hell yeah!
I'm gonna kill it!
Oh you know I'll
be back, bro!
Bring it on.
Hmph. We are okay.
We are totally
pumped up! Alright!
Don't spoil the child
by sparing the rod!
That's not how that goes.
We're gonna pass
this thing
without even
breaking a sweat!
Now that's the spirit!
Ms. Fumio and I will be
taking care of things here.
OH! Your job is to do
the best that you can!
(Group cheers)
[HISAKO]
And that's about it.
You depart in three days.
The students will
assemble at 6:00 am.
I see.
That will be all, Hisako.
(Rooster crows)
[ALL]
Uh...
I have a
stomach ache...
Ah don't worry, I'm sure
it won't be all bad.
All right!
Let's do this, guys!
All aboard the Hell‐bound
Training Camp Express!
Nothing is gonna get
in my way now!
(Rattling)
(Gasps)
[AOKI and SATO]
That's awesome!
[MEGUMI]
Uh... THIS is where
we'll be training?
[SOMA]
This school sure has
money, all right.
Do they own
this giant hotel?
Well it might shock you.
But Tohtsuki runs all
the hotels around here.
Ha! That doesn't
shock me at all!
I heard that a dozen or more
are actually functioning under
the Tohtsuki Resort brand...
and that a lot of the former
graduates are currently
working in their kitchens.
If you stay for the night,
I've heard it can cost
up to 80 thousand yen.
(Girls scream)
That's like rent money
for a whole entire month!
That doesn't shock me either!
But you sure do
LOOK kinda shocked.
Okay then, we get to stay
here the whole time, right?
It's time for some luxury!
If you can survive
each day's agenda.
(Blows raspberry)
Shun, can't you
just let a girl
live in her dream world?
I'm keeping
it real.
Come on. We have
to assemble
as soon as we put
our luggage down.
[YUKI]
Yeah, fine.
(Nervous grunts)
This place is eerily quiet.
You wouldn't think almost 1,000
students are gathered here.
The calm before the storm...
It's coming. The
training‐camp‐from‐hell
is about to begin.
I wonder how many of us
gathered here will make it.
(Nervous whimper)
Whoa! Hey,
it's Meat‐Meat!
Uh, hey, Soma!
It has been a while...
How are you doin?.
Soma, don't you
feel nervous at all?
Uh, you probably should be
calling her by that nickname!
Huh? But she likes it
when I call her that.
Right, Meat‐Meat?
Huh?! What would give
you that idea?!
See? Look how
happy she is.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
That transfer student
is a total d‐bag...
(Murmurs)
You be careful, Soma.
Hm? Of what?
[CHAPELLE]
Good morning, everyone!
I will now briefly go over
ze details of zis required
training camp.
You will be staying here
for six days.
And split into groups...
you will tackle various
food‐related challenges,
as well as test ze limits
of your stamina.
Any student who falls below ze
standard set by ze instructors
will receive a failing grade.
You will be returned to ze
academy, and zen you will
be asked to leave.
(Gulp)
We have invited some
guest instructors
who will act as judges
for your challenges.
Guests? What
kinda guests?
Though zey are incredibly busy,
zey have gathered
here for zis event!
Please welcome ze graduates
of Tohtsuki Academy!
(Mass shock)
Those are actual
graduates!
And they all
came here for us!
[SATO]
Dude, they must
be like geniuses
to have actually
graduated from Tohtsuki.
[SCHOOLBOY]
This is awesome...
Hm?
[KOJIRO]
You there.
In the ninth row
from the front.
The young man with
the cut over his brow.
Hm?
[KOJIRO]
No, next to you.
Huh?
[KOJIRO]
Yes, you.
You're expelled.
You may leave now.
Wha‐?!
Your hair product has
a citrus aroma to it.
[KOJIRO]
That would mask the scent
of your cooking, yes?
Obviously, I know it's
important to look good.
A swarthy‐looking chef will
lessen the appeal of his food.
Perhaps next time,
you should choose an
unscented hair product.
I'm expelled?!
Seriously?!
For something like that?
"Something like that" can be
enough to lose customers.
Ya little troll.
Are you out to destroy
my restaurant?
Hnn!
That'll be all.
Get out of my sight.
Uh...
(Whimpers)
Who was that?
Chef Kojiro Shinomiya!
He's the first Japanese chef
to ever win France's
Brousse‐Poiret Award!
And over there...
is Chef Fuyumi Mizuhara
from "Ristorante F"!
And from sushi restaurant
"Ginza Hinowa,"
Chef Hitoshi Sekimori!
Oh wow! All these
chefs are featured in top
magazines almost every month!
[GOTODA]
Just as unassuming
as a Dutch clover!
[ZENJI]
From Auberge "Trésor,"
that's Donato Gotoda!
I was put on this earth just so
I could lay my eyes upon you.
Care to go back
to my auberge...
where we can talk
til the sunrise?
Huh? I, uh...
S'cuse me what was that?
[HINAKO]
Oh leave her alone,
Chef Gotoda.
Hmm. Hinako...
[ZENJI]
That's Hinako Inui from
the Japanese restaurant
"Kiri‐no‐ya"!
(Giggle) Oh sweetie,
that must have been
very frightening for you.
You certainly are
adorable, aren't you?
Goodness, you look
like a tasty little
dish indeed.
Huh? Huh?!
Hinako...
(Angry growl)
[GOTODA]
Master Chapelle is scowling.
Let's go back.
[HINAKO]
Oh!
Come by my
restaurant anytime.
HOOKAY...
That's him! Oh my God!
[ZENJI]
He took the top spot
on his graduation exam
with the highest
score in history!
That man turned down
over 800 offers
from first‐class restaurants
all over the world
(Crowd gasps)
just to be in his
current position.
He's the Executive Chef of the
Tohtsuki Resort chain and sits
on the board of directors:
Gin Dojima!
I am freaking out!
The elite chefs making a name
for Japanese cuisine...
are all right here
in front of us!
Welcome, students...
to the illustrious
Tohtsuki Resort.
All the graduates you see
before you are chef‐owners,
masters of their domains.
For the six days you're here,
we are going to be treating
you exactly as if you were
employees at our restaurants.
Do you know what that means?
Anyone who does not
perform to our liking...
is done!
Meaning, you're expelled.
(Gulp)
[GIN]
As you have seen,
your teachers have the power
to send you home at any moment.
I wish you good fighting.
Now then, you know
your groups...
Get moving!
Even though we're split up,
let's do our best.
I'm stuck in the same
group as you again?!
Got a problem
with that, bro?!
I'll see ya.
Later!
Oh, let's play poker in
Zenji's room later on.
Don't even think
about using my room
for any of your bullcrap
at a time like THIS!
[RYOKO]
So, you wanna taste?
[YUKI]
I sure do!
(Gasp)
[HINAKO]
Okay, looks like we're all here.
For this exercise, I would
like to have you pair up
and work in teams.
You'll be in the same
pairs as your first lecture
of the semester,
so please head to
your labelled stations.
Thank the freakin' comsos!
I'm so glad to be
paired with you again.
Yeah, it's gonna
be great.
You're Soma Yukihira,
aren't you?
Huh?
Yeah, that
would be me.
Hehehe.
Uh, that's over 10 seconds
of foot‐grinding.
I'm guessing you're trying
to get my attention.
Yes, I am.
[TAKUMI]
I've been hoping to cross
paths with you, buddy...
But I never thought
I'd get the chance
on our very
first challenge!
I look forward
to crushing you!
Just like how
I crushed your shoe.
Uhh...
Um, guys?
This is already
a difficult camp!
It is neither the time nor the
place for trying to pick fights!
Now I can finally
destroy you!
I'm glad it gets to be
me who's gonna do it!
Is that so?
Well I'm real happy for you.
But if you don't move your foot,
I'm gonna break it off.
[HINAKO]
Okay, everyone!
[ALL]
Huh?
I will be sitting right
here the whole time.
If there's anything you don't
understand, please ask.
Um, Chef?
You haven't given
out any instructions
on what you'd like
for us to cook, yet. Uh...
Oh, I guess not.
Okay!
Um, my challenge
for you today...
Is to use the
ingredients here to
make a dish emphasizing
traditional
Japanese cooking.
(Confused murmurs)
[SCHOOLBOY]
"Ingredients here"?
But there isn't a supply
of ingredients here.
Well of course there is.
The bounty of nature's
at your disposal...
and a clear stream with
a wealth of options.
[HINAKO]
You have seasonings, oil,
and cooking utensils.
Feel free to also use the
fishing equipment.
The surrounding area is our
own private land. You can
go as far as the fence.
Crossing the fence will be an
automatic failing grade.
You'll get your ingredients
solely from within the
designated area,
and then cook with only them.
As long as you make a dish
that satisfies my palate,
you will pass.
You have two hours
to complete your meal.
Now get going and
begin your journey.
(Squeal)
Huh? So did it just start?!
I think so!
This lady's bonkers!
I guess first we have to see
if we can catch some fish!
If we can get ourselves
some sweetfish we can do
a salt broil, right?!
Is sweetfish even
in season now?
Who cares, we only
have two hours!
Hurry!
(Frantic screaming)
[TAKUMI]
I challenge you, Soma.
What's that?
You want to challenge me?
It's time that we resolve
whose cooking is superior.
Chef, I'd like for
YOU to settle this.
Huh?
Tell us which of our dishes
is more delicious.
I'd like your
impartial judgment!
Huh? Why would I do that?
That has nothing to do
with this challenge, so no.
[TAKUMI]
Huh? Oh. O‐oh right.
(Cheeky laugh)
Oh man, your face!
Chill out! You don't have
to get all worked up,
it's making things
uncomfortable.
(Angry growl)
(Laugh)
AHAHAHA! You're such a dork!
That was so uncool, Bro!
Shut up! Why are YOU
laughing at me?!
"Bro"? Are these
two siblings?
Genetics are weird...
You! I will not allow
my masterful skills
to lose against you!
I will make a dish that
makes yours look like snot!
You understand me, Soma?!
[ISAMI]
Come on,
let's go already.
[SOMA]
What was that
all about?
Ah! Soma, we should
get going, too!
I'll see you later!
(Giggle)
[HINAKO]
People's thinking narrows when
they're placed in an unfamiliar
situation.
Dammit! I can't
catch crap!
Pipe down, dumbass!
You'll scare the fish!
Okay! We can make a
meuniere out of this.
But we don't have
any access to flour!
[SCHOOLBOY]
I told you to go out
there and bring back
some bamboo shoots!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
I did, but I
couldn't find any!
Their wits are dulled.
They misjudge
their actions.
This challenge is a very
basic personality test.
Anyone who cannot persevere
through something like this,
has no place at Tohtsuki.
Gaahh...
We really need to hurry up
and catch something
so we can start cooking!
What should our
menu be, Soma?
If it's char or rainbow trout
we could do a salt broil.
Or a soy simmer!
Ah! And we've gotta start
thinking about our presentation!
And we need to start looking
for some greens!
The thing is, I'm thinkin'
everyone's probably gonna
go that route, right?
I wanna change things up
a bit if I can.
It's a bit late
to start doing that!
We just have to be quick
and finish up our dish!
I know, but I
still want to try...
Hm.
AH!
You got one!
[MEGUMI]
Thank goodness.
We managed to get some pretty
good sized fish, huh?
Sure did. Now it's just a
question of how to cook them.
[SOMA]
Well hello...
"Mr. Impartial Judgment!"
Shut up! Just shut up!
Heh! Looks like you're one
of the lemmings too.
Huh?
[TAKUMI]
Well, well, well.
The theme is Japanese,
so everyone is gonna use fish?
Seems a little bit
narrow‐minded if you ask me.
(Angry grunts)
What's with
the attitude?
What are you
idiots using?
Hmph!
Huh?
Know what this is?
We're doing duck!
Uh. You were able
to get duck?!
And that's not
all there was.
There were a few chickens
and rabbits out there too.
Of course, I'm not surprised
none of you bothered to look
beyond the fishies.
Now we're all stuck making
the same damn thing!
We don't even know
how to prep those
ingredients as it is.
Out of the way.
Move it, Soma.
Huh?
(Light gasp)
Isami!
It's go time.
(Grunting and laughing)
He's slicing the
breast and thigh meat
with such precision!
He's so fast, and
he's not damaging any
of the organs at all!
[MEGUMI]
Truly skillful knife work...
Yeah? Can I do
something for ya?
Uh, no! I was just
noticing how good you
are with that knife.
Aw you think so?
Well, my brother over there
is three times faster than me.
(Gasp)
[MEGUMI]
There are no breaks
in his movement.
There's no wasted
motion whatsoever!
Who on Earth is he?
Yeah, looks like this guy
has what it takes.
[SOMA]
Those are hands that have
obviously worked the line.
Forno accendere!
[TAKUMI]
We haven't
introduced ourselves.
My name is Takumi Aldini.
This is my twin brother.
I'm Isami Aldini.
The two of us have already
worked in the kitchen
of our local trattoria.
"Trattoria"?
[TAKUMI]
It's Italian.
It's a casual,
high‐volume bistro.
[TAKUMI]
You and I aren't
that different.
I, as you, am a chef working
to protect my family restaurant.
Unlike what you said
at the commencement:
[SOMA]
I still don't plan on
losing to a bunch of wannabes
who've never even stood in
front of a customer before.
You billed yourself as a pro
amongst the rest.
And as a fellow pro, I can't
let myself lose to you.
Aldini vs. Yukihira...
I'll show you who
the real chef is here!
(Swish)
[SOMA]
Sounds fun!
I've been hoping for
some competition!
(Shocked cries)
Well, in that case...
AH!
[SCHOOLBOY]
What the heck is that?!
A mezzaluna.
It means "half moon,"
and is primarily used
in Italian cooking.
[TAKUMI]
Here we go...
Tritare!
He's totally mastered that
strange knife thing!
He's reducing the ingredients
to paste in seconds!
The duck is just
about done, Takumi.
I'll have the salsa ready.
Gotcha! I'm finished
on my end as well.
[TAKUMI]
Okay!
Hehe. GGRRRR!
AHHH!
[TAKUMI]
Tre...
Due...
Uno...
[BOTH in Italian]
Fine!
You guys finished
first, did you?
Speed is one of the
sacred hallmarks of
proper Italian cooking.
[SCHOOLGIRL]
That was way
too fast!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
And they still had time
to dress the duck!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
That didn't even
take an hour!
[TAKUMI]
This is an herb‐grilled duck.
With a fresh green
sauce on the side.
Buon appetito.
[HINAKO]
Well then...
Let's have a taste.
The duck is so rich,
brimming with the
taste of the wild.
Then there's a burst of
artful refreshment that
elevates the flavor!
MMM!
The combination of
manliness and elegance
forms wave after wave,
reverberating to the
depths of the stomach.
(Opera singing)
[HINAKO]
It's like a... Like an
aria of water fowl!
I want this duck...
to embrace me!
(Singing intensifies)
Aw man! Check out that
green sauce he made...
It's a salsa verde!
[SCHOOLBOY]
It's got anchovies and
chopped Italian parsley.
That's a staple
of ITALIAN cooking.
What are you
guys thinking?
The theme was
Japanese cooking!
That has got to be
an automatic fail!
No. It IS Japanese.
The sauce is salt‐broiled
char and uruka entrails
rather than anchovies.
(Shocked gasps)
I seem to recall that
uruka generally takes more
than a week to prepare,
but you made this on
the spot, correct?
Yes.
[TAKUMI]
We washed the
sweetfish entrails
and boiled them in sake,
then added mirin,
soy sauce, and salt.
Doing so, we made an impromptu,
rich‐tasting uruka with just
a touch of bitterness.
(Astonished murmurs)
[HINAKO]
But that's not all you
did to convert it, did you?
Rather than traditional
Italian parsley, they used
diced chives in its place.
By using that, they made a
refreshing green sauce!
Also, instead of garlic,
they used a citrus and
pepper paste,
giving it a very Japanese
flavor.
The unique elements
enhanced the whole dish.
I like to call it a
Japanese‐style salsa verde
using an improvised
uruka as its base!
They were able to make a
Japanese‐style Italian sauce?
Dude. I'm drooling
just hearing about it.
It's incredible!
I can't believe they were able
to combine so many ingredients
from just this small area!
Unlike Japan, Italy has a long
history of eating meat.
And in Tuscany,
where these two are from,
duck, rabbit, and boar
are often served,
depending on the season.
That must be where
they learned to break
down and prepare duck.
The breast is so rich
because it was grilled
in a glaze of soy sauce,
spicy mustard, black pepper,
and honey.
And the salsa is the
perfect complement.
This salsa verde duck was
infused with Japanese elements
in a measured and creative way.
A flawless combination
of Japanese technique
and imagination.
Takumi Aldini... Isami Aldini...
You both pass!
Grazie!
[MEGUMI]
Even with limited ingredients,
he was able to use his wits to
come up with some amazing food.
That guy reminds
me of...
He's just like Soma!
(Ending Song)
Ahh! Merveilleuse!
Erina Nakiri, you pass!
[ERINA]
No surprise.
[TAKUMI]
Next time on Food Wars,
the ninth course:
"The Breading that
Showcases the Mountains"
(Takumi and Isami laugh)
[BOTH]
Grazie!
I will crush you...
In the face!
You are so
uncool, dude.