[CHEF 1]
And this is the last item.
[ERINA]
Hmm...
Mph.
(Relaxed sigh)
(Light laugh)
(Grunt)
Ah?
Waagh!
[ERINA]
Disgusting!
[CHEF 1]
Uwagh! Aahh!
Ow, ow, OW!
[ERINA]
Now seriously. I can't believe
you've all made it this far
putting out such
nauseating slop.
Especially,
that oyster porridge.
Ugh! It was...
like taking a bath with a
sweaty Western Lowland Gorilla!
[ALL]
Huh?
[CHEF 2]
That's uh... pretty obscure...
[CHEF 3]
Her sense of taste is
quite a bit different
from ordinary people.
Start over. It looks like
you took a shortcut or two
with the MISE EN PLACE.
Uh!
[ERINA]
Listen.
I know your group is trying
to expand its business,
so you're looking to make things
more efficient and everything.
But even so,
it does you no good to violate
and pollute a person's tongue
with something like THIS?
Ah! I‐I, uh... Uh...
[GROUP]
We are so very sorry,
Miss Erina!
(Opening Song)
Ah...
It's time for you to go,
too, Soma.
Come back once you've
learned what you're made of.
(Speechless gasp)
[SOMA]
Man, I stick out
like a sore thumb.
Jeez. All these other kids
have butlers and bodyguards!
[JOICHIRO]
And don't forget, son,
you'll be attending one
of the best cooking schools
in the country.
It's highly competitive
and the graduation rate
is less than 10%.
Which means most of the people
you meet won't last a month.
Uh!
[JOICHIRO]
Well, good luck, Soma.
That school will‐
[MCFLEE]
Hey, Joe!
[JOICHIRO]
I'll be with you
just in a moment, sir
So where are you
working now, anyway?
(Car horns blaring)
[JOICHIRO]
I'm in New York City.
At the Manhattan Royal Hotel,
the VIP reception hall.
Huh?!
Not sure how long
I'll be here, though.
Man, Joe!
I am so glad you came
back to old New York!
We have really
missed you, my man!
(Laughs)
You've got to keep the
excitement down, Dr. McFlee.
Y'know, the blood pressure!
(Hearty laugh)
(Heartbeat)
Oh god! Oh yes...!
I had to leave my office
in Congress after I'd
gotten deathly ill,
So I thought if I could just eat
Yukihira's cooking one last
time, I'd have no regrets.
(Male Aide whimpers)
But now I can't stop and I stuff
my face here every chance I get.
(Chuckle)
Sir, I beg you.
May we come again?
Mmm...
Oh please say yes, Sir!
(Crowd screams)
Is this where I
can find Yukihira?!
Please let's go back,
High Priest!
You're in the
middle of fasting.
You need to set an
example for the rest‐
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
You're saying I can't eat
Yukihira's food when it's
right in front of me?!
Nay!
I shall abandon my faith!
[ACOLYTES]
High Priest!
(High priest laughs)
[JOICHIRO]
My buddy and I went
to India first,
then Italy and Spain.
I flew in to New York yesterday.
I plan on staying here in
America and cooking for a while.
[SOMA]
Huh? I can't even keep up
with what you're saying.
[JOICHIRO]
I'm doing this as a
favor to a friend.
So, listen to me, Soma...
The thought of you surviving
that school till graduation
and getting better than me,
is almost comical!
(Tense inhale)
[SOMA]
I'm friggin' doin' it!
Alright. How about I share
with you a few secrets
to improving your
cooking skills‐
(Phone hangs up)
Huh?
He hung up on me, dammit.
[HIGH PRIEST]
Where is Yukihira?!
(Unintelligible)
[JOICHIRO]
Alright! Coming!
Listen, Soma.
The trick to being
a good chef...
...is the right woman...
a woman who will
make you a better man.
Better at cooking.
Better at everything.
[ERINA]
Well? What do I
have next?
This, ma'am.
Judging the
transfer exams? Hmph.
I didn't know joining
the council would mean
doing this kind
of menial labor.
I guess I'll head over
there after I've changed.
[SOMA]
Dammit! He thinks it's
"a joke," huh?
Well, I WILL make
it to the very end!
(Thud)
[SOMA]
Agh!
Ah!
I'm sorry! I didn't
mean to do that.
[YOSHIAKI]
Oh, not to worry.
You're trying to transfer
here as well, are you?
Please, have a seat.
Thanks.
[YOSHIAKI]
Tohtsuki's middle‐school
division is announcing
their advancement
exam results today.
Plus, students from other
middle schools, like us,
are here for the transfer exam.
I'm Yoshiaki Nikaido.
My family runs a prominent
French restaurant.
Huh, that's crazy,
what a coincidence.
We have a family
restaurant, too.
Yeah well... It may
not be a coincidence.
Huh?
[YOSHIAKI]
That boy over there...
he's the heir to a
nationwide restaurant chain.
The other is the son
of a major wholesaler
that distributes
fish throughout Kanto.
Most everyone here
works in food.
All on the path to be
restauranteurs.
Ooh.
What's the name of your
family's restaurant?
Ah, it's called
"Yukihira."
Yukihira...
Gourmet, I'm assuming?
(Laughs)
Nah nah, it's
nothin' that fancy.
It's just a little diner
located in Shitamachi‐
Oof!
A diner?
Gah!
You wretched,
lowly plebian.
You may no longer
sit next to ME!
You listen and
listen well:
This school is not a place
for scrounging Neandertals!
This is sacred ground where
only those who live in the
world of fine cuisine
may dare to learn
and achieve!
[YOSHIAKI]
You don't belong here!
Tohtsuki is a
Fine Dining Academy!
Simpleton riff‐raff
like yourself won't even
get past the written exam‐
[SOMA]
Hey!
Don't start looking down
your nose at me, pal.
You don't know anything
about me, alright!
Ah!
[BODYGUARDS]
Young sir! Are you okay?!
(Flabbergasted)
(Growl)
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Look at that.
Someone from a diner actually
thinks he can transfer here.
This should be hilarious.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
What a joke!
That guy needs to
learn his place!
I mean seriously.
[SOMA]
This could be pretty rough.
If people are like this
right off the bat,
how hoity‐toity is this
judge gonna be?
(Intimidated murmurs)
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
Is that...
Is it really her...?!
[SCHOOLBOY 4]
Uh... yeah...
Hm?
All potential transfers,
I'll be overseeing your
transfer exams today.
My name is Erina Nakiri.
A girl?
And look, she's wearing
an Academy uniform.
[SOMA]
SHE'S gonna be the judge?
[ERINA]
Alright, what is
their assignment today?
[HISAKO]
I'll read it now.
"First, we will be
administering group interviews
so as to review your
applications.
After that, you will be asked
to prepare three dishes.
Those who proceed‐"
[ERINA] Hmph!
Uh!
Seriously?
Uh...
Alright then...
[ERINA]
Bring the cooking station here.
[HISAKO]
Uh, yes, Ma'am!
(Shocked murmers)
[SCHOOLBOY 5]
Ingredients?
[SCHOOLBOY 6]
What's going on?
[ERINA]
Your main ingredient
will be eggs.
Make me one proper dish.
Those whose plate
impresses me may transfer.
All others will be forever
banned from the Academy.
(Nervous reactions)
[SCHOOLBOY 7]
What? Forever?
[ERINA]
Now, all of you...
You have just
one minute starting now
to decide your fate.
Now's your chance
to give up and leave.
Huh? One minute?!
I‐I abstain! I'm out!
[SOMA]
Huh...?
Hey, wait!
Ah!
Why are you
running away?
Are you kidding me?
Don't tell me you
don't know who she is!
Hm? No clue. Tell me.
[YOSHIAKI]
That's Erina Nakiri,
harbinger of the greatest
palate known to man...
She's known as
the God Tongue!
[SOMA]
Huh?
[YOSHIAKI]
Children usually
start talking
between the ages
of one and two,
But not her...
when she was just
three months old,
she spoke her
very first words:
Hm...
Oh, God.
This lacks flavor.
[YOSHIAKI]
She quickly developed
such talent, that from
a very young age,
she was asked to taste‐test
for famous restaurants
all across the country.
All the biggest names
in the culinary world
are clients of hers!
Any critique she gives
will spread throughout
the food industry!
If she tastes anything
less than perfection,
she will tell you you're
a talentless hack!
And your life as a chef will be
completely ruined forever!
AHH! Guh!
Ahhh!
[ERINA]
As expected, a bunch of
dimwits with no promise.
This is a
pointless exercise.
These recruits are always
a bunch of drooling monkeys.
Is that all we have left
on our schedule for today?
Uh, yes.
Then I will be going
to go to my room
so I can work on
a new dish.
(Gasp)
A new dish by Miss Erina?!
(Whimper)
Aw, what is it,
Hisako?
Your face says that
you want something.
Uh... I uh... I just...
(Whimper)
Are you trying
to tell me
you want the right
to taste my food?
I... I do! Please!
My, aren't you a
greedy little girl.
(Laugh)
Oh no!
I'm so sorry,
Miss Erina!
Well okay, but not until
we make our report...
zero candidates passed.
Uh‐huh!
Excuse me!
[BOTH] Ah!
So I can just make
whatever I want?
Ah!
What?
[ERINA]
Someone is actually...
challenging me?
AAHHHH!
So long as you
incorporate the eggs...
you're free to make
whatever you like.
But are you really sure
you want to do this?
It's still okay to quit and‐
Man, I was kinda
worried!
I was like, "What if I
flunk out without even
getting to make anything?!"
GET AWAY FROM HER!
Guh!
Do you know who
you just touched?
Not really.
[HISAKO]
This is none other
than the top student
in the Middle‐School
Division...
and the youngest
member in history
ever seated at the table
for the Council of Ten...
This is Erina Nakiri!
[SOMA]
Dude, I've only seen one
of these knives on TV!
[BOTH]
You need to pay attention!
Hm?
Look, I will ask you again:
Do you really intend on
trying to take my exam?
Uh... Well, uh...
You just have to say
it tastes good, right?
(Sheen)
Then of course,
let's do it.
Who is this guy?
Here's his file.
[ERINA]
Soma Yukihira...
Your family runs a diner.
Pedestrian food from
a pedestrian chef.
[ERINA]
He doesn't appreciate my
pedigree, does he?
(Heavy panting)
Much like a stray dog
doesn't realize the value
of a precious gemstone.
Hm. Well, you will have the
honor of me tasting your food...
I'm sure it will be a
meal fit for a trucker.
I think I'd like to...
...serve you a little
specialty from my family shop!
Coming right up!
[SOMA]
Just gimme a
few minutes.
(Chopping)
Eggs are a universal staple
in Japan, China, and
throughout the West.
[HISAKO]
Miss Erina tastes egg
dishes from high‐end
restaurants every day.
What sort of dish can
he possibly make?
(Hissing and boiling)
(Beating eggs)
It seems like he's scrambling
the eggs, but...
I can't see the
finished product at all.
[ERINA]
Soma Yukihira,
what in God's name
are you up to?
Huh?
You've been watching me
but STILL can't figure
it out? Hoo‐hoo‐hoo!
I can flunk you
right here and now!
Listen to me: I don't
have time to spend on
some churned up gruel.
Let's be clear, to pass
you'll need to make a dish
suitable for MY godly tongue!
'Kay, fine. I'll tell you.
I'm making No. 8 on the Yukihira
Japanese Eatery's secret menu!
(Clack)
"Secret menu"?
That won't make it
taste any better.
Furikake rice.
(Shake shake)
Uh...
(Wind blowing)
(Slam)
[ERINA]
Don't play with me!
You can't fake it, you're
a glorified fry cook.
I had better things
to do today.
[HISAKO] Miss Erina?
[SOMA] Of course...
this isn't any
normal furikake.
Ah?
What I'm making for you is...
Transforming Furikake Rice!
"Transforming Furikake"?
[SOMA]
It should be done
just about any second now.
Soma Yukihira...
Just what sort of food cart
trick do you intend to make?
Hm...
Please... enjoy!
(Ding)
[BOTH]
Uhh...
Yep. As I thought...
He has nothing
to offer!
Hm!
Ugh...
Hah...
It just looks like
normal furikake.
This is the work of an
untrained amateur.
It doesn't even
make me hungry.
[ERINA]
My palate is such that I'm
called the "God Tongue"...
and only experienced,
extravagant,
nuanced dishes
grace my dining table.
I am accustomed to refined
worldly cuisine.
Something you cannot
understand...
Demonstrated by you
serving me something like THIS.
The exam is over.
Miss Erina!
But, this dish hasn't
transformed into
its true form yet.
Ah?
And what do you
mean by that?
Hm!
(Gasp)
[ERINA]
There's something
underneath the egg.
(Gasp)
Well, take a look.
The fun of furikake...
is when it's on top
of rice, right?
Now then...
Uh!
(Twinkling)
[SOMA]
It's done.
(Jiggle)
(Astonished gasps)
Ah!
[ERINA]
The heat from the rice
is melting it!
And as it melts, it coats
more and more of the rice!
Uh!
What is this aroma?
Is it chicken?
The delicate scent of
slow‐simmered chicken
is gradually building.
I get it...
Transforming Furikake Rice!
It is completely different
than it started!
I have got to find out
what it tastes like!
I will grant you this...
I will go ahead and take a bite.
Heh.
[ERINA]
One.
Shut up and give me
that bowl, you idiot!
Order up!
(Sharp gasp)
(Slow piano music)
Om.
Mm.
(Heartbeat)
Ah!
(Gasp)
What's going on?
I was just tasting it!
I forgot to judge it!
Oh! What is that texture?
[SOMA]
Hang on, now...
Are you going in
for a second bite?
I thought I heard something
about you only needing one.
Mm... What is your problem?!
Do not interrupt the God
Tongue while she is at work,
do you understand me?!
I'm just kidding.
I need silence!
Relax and enjoy.
(Dramatic music)
Nikogori?
We have a winner!
Those little
jiggly cubes
are made from
chicken wings.
[SOMA]
Nikogori is meat or fish broth
with lots of gelatin
so it hardens into a kind of
jelly when cooled.
I simmered the chicken
wings in fish seasoning,
sake, and mild soy sauce.
Chilled the broth to
harden it, then sliced it
up all nice and fine.
[SOMA]
When it goes on top
of the hot rice,
the broth from the
chicken wings melts,
binding it with the
soft‐scrambled egg.
[ERINA]
So this nikogori is
a soup, so to speak...
rich and infused with the
flavor from the chicken.
Wait a minute.
The richness and saltiness
of the smooth broth
draws out the gentle
sweetness of the fluffy egg.
With each bite, fluffiness
and velvetiness caress
the inside of my mouth!
The melted nikogori
dramatically elevates the
sumptuousness of the egg.
This is unlike any dish
I've ever tasted.
It's a wave of flavors
completely unknown to me!
Well, whatcha think, huh?
Ah!
Are you glad you didn't
leave without trying it?
Ah! Be quiet!
I am not
finished judging!
With originality
and creativity,
Ah!
you can elevate even
the most everyday dishes.
THAT is the essence
of Yukihira!
[ERINA]
No...
I live in the heavenly
tower of deliciousness.
I cannot approve this.
(Sly laugh)
[ERINA]
Food made by the very picture
of the common man!
I can't... approve...
I can't...
I mustn't... approve!
Ahh...
(Gasp)
(Moan)
Ooh!
This... flavor!
It's as if... It's as if...
I'm being lovingly stroked
by buttery angel's wings!
Ahhhh...
(Angels laugh)
Uh! Ahh!
(Laughing continues)
Ah!
Go away!
Get away from me!
Stay away, you little freaks!
AHH!
(Choral music)
[ERINA]
I cannot approve this! I can't!
My tongue...
My body...
I can't let them
respond to this!
Unh!
(Whimper)
[SOMA]
You're right...
I'm just a piddly
low‐life diner cook.
And you may be the princess
of the food world
and possess the "God Tongue"...
But you know,
if you just sit at the table
playing the critic,
you'll never grow
in the kitchen.
[SOMA]
No what I mean?
(Light grunt)
Miss Erina...
Well, whaddya say?
(Fluttering breath)
[SOMA]
Yukihira‐style furikake rice:
Is it delicious or not?
Say it!
(Struggling)
Hmm?
(More struggling)
(Light gasp)
It's...
Uh‐huh...
...disgusting!
WHA‐?!
[ERINA]
Who does this guy think he is?!
He is so full of it!
So disrespectful!
Toward ME, Erina Nakiri!
Unforgivable!
Ugh!
(Whine)
Soma Yukihira...
(Cocky laugh)
This Academy has no need
for people like you!
(Poof)
Hello, this is Erina.
Yes that's right.
Please inform
the Academy director,
my grandfather...
That in today's
transfer test...
not a single one of the
applicants were acceptable.
Gehh...
(Ending Song)
Hmm...
Hm!
(Laugh)
(Massive laugh)
Hmm!
[ERINA]
Next time, you will enjoy
the third course of Food Wars:
"That Chef Doesn't Smile"
Try to keep up.
[HIGH PRIEST]
Ohoho! Om! Umph! AHAHAHA!