[SOMA]
Hey, Isshiki! We're back!
Ah, Welcome home everyone!
I'm glad to see you've
all made it through the
training camp from hell.
Each of you did
just splendidly...
Huh?
ATATATATA!
Did you miss us?
Soma?!
You've really
bulked up!
I'm guessing your challenges
were quite difficult.
(Heavy chewing and grunting)
Megumi?!
Is that you, Megumi?
You seem a bit on
the gloomy side...
Shaddap, ya loser!
HUH?!
Heh‐heh...
Whaddya say we beat this
skinny little wuss
to a bloody pulp.
Let's snap his scrawny,
little neck!
Please do not disrespect
your elders like that.
I don't take kindly to it!
Hey Shun. What happened to
your once‐charming hairstyle?!
Bushy.
Uh!
Hang on, you guys.
Where's Zenji?
I don't see him anywhere.
What happened to him?
The only thing we could find...
were these.
Oh God... Not him!
Oh, Zenji, my boy!
(Sobbing)
HUUH!
Ooh...
Oh wow, man, what a nightmare.
Today's only the third
day of the training camp.
Please make it back, everyone.
GRR!
This is awful!
Make it all again!
Mm‐mm! Megumi Tadokoro, you
may clean up your station.
You pass!
Hah! Thank you very much!
(Giggle)
Ahh! Hey, look out!
Oh! I'm sorry!
Great job, Megumi.
But we still have
a long way to go.
Hm.
[SOMA]
I'm not there yet.
Not at all.
Not even close.
All right!
I've gotta hone my skills.
I must get better!
(Opening Song)
(Grunts)
You act like some sorta
queen around here...
Well you can't
keep it up forever.
Thanks so much
for the advice.
I will certainly try to
keep that in mind, okay? z
The sad ramblings
of the lower class
are very helpful.
(Chuckle)
(Yuki groans)
Today was absolutely
horrendous again!
Ugh! I wanna get back to my
luxury suite and sleep.
We still have two
more days left.
[RYOKO]
I think we can still pull
it off though, you guys.
Hmm? There's no
assigned bedtime curfew
set for tonight.
Hm...
Yeah, you're right.
[YUKI]
It's gotta be, like, a
printing error, right?
(PA chimes on)
All students of
Tohtsuki Academy:
At 10:00 PM, that's
one hour from now,
you are to report to the main
banquet hall dressed in your
school uniforms.
Once again, that's 10pm.
(Shocked reactions)
What the huh?
Are you kidding me?
GAH!
Hm?
[SOMA]
There sure are a lot
less of us now, huh?
(Whimper)
[RYOKO]
Everyone looks pretty beat.
I wonder what they're
planning for tonight.
[TAKUMI]
Soma!
Huh?
You are a moron!
How could you be
so full of yourself
to challenge a graduate
to a Food War?!
I am not letting you
leave the academy until
we've settled things.
Once and for all!
Who the hell are
you supposed to be??
Who exactly are you?
How'd you find out?
That was supposed
to be a secret.
Everyone's talking about it,
you unbelievable idiot!
Wait a second...if you're still
here, then that must mean...
You mean... you beat
Kojiro Shinomiya?!
You actually did it?
Uh!
Not quite. I totally lost it.
Huh? You lost
to him? Oh...
Yeah. Could you not
talk about it anymore?
Oh I don't think so!
What on Earth
happened in there?!
Look.
Huh?
[SCHOOLBOY]
Miss Erina!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
It's HER!
[GIN]
Everyone direct your
attention toward the stage.
There is but one reason you
have been called here:
for me to inform you
of tomorrow's challenge.
Tomorrow?
But why do they need to tell
us about it the night before?
[GIN]
Ladies and gentlemen...
Your challenge is to create
a new breakfast item
befitting our guests
here at Tohtsuki Resort.
Breakfast is the face
of our hotel.
It is an important meal
that represents the start
of our guests' day.
Present something that
gives the table an air
of invigorated radiance.
Something that cannot
be ignored nor forgotten.
Make a single dish,
one that gives a sense
of wonder for the day.
Your main ingredient
will be eggs.
You are allowed to prepare
any style of cuisine...
but it must be presented
in the buffet‐fashion.
Judgment will begin
at 6:00 am tomorrow.
Be ready to present your dish
for tasting by that time.
(Shocked murmurs)
Hmmm?
I think I might have
just misheard that.
He did say 6:00 PM, right?
No he didn't...
he totally said 6 "AM"
They're trying to kill us!
We're not going to
get any sleep tonight!
Use your time however
you see fit.
You may use the kitchen
to test your new dishes...
or you may rest up
back in your rooms.
But I'll see you all
bright and early.
You're dismissed!
(Mass groans)
My entire body
is a complete wreck!
I can't think straight
under these conditions!
I'm starting to
lose my mind!
Finally, we have ourselves
a worthwhile challenge.
Just you wait, Soma Yukihira.
I am going to show you
the ultimate breakfast...
Where staple Italian egg
dishes are interpreted
through the incomparable
Aldini techniques!
Hahaaa...
So tell me, what exactly
are "staple Italian
egg dishes" like?
Heh!
It's like this.
You fold shredded cheese
or different kinds of
vegetables into the eggs...
What are you telling
him for, Isami?!
Come on...
Are you trying to give away
all our family secrets?!
That's enough, come on we're
going back to our room!
Yeah, okay.
So looks like it'll
be eggs again.
Hey, wasn't that was the
theme for my entrance exam?
AH!
Your main ingredient
will be eggs.
Make me one proper dish.
Order up!
Seems like yesterday...
Good times.
Do not talk to me
like we're friends!
Ugh! Let me warn you right now:
You can't put out such haphazard
cooking this time around.
Not unless you want the judges
to laugh you out of school.
But you ate it like
you thought it was
the best thing ever.
What?! As if! I believe
I told you it was
vile and disgusting!
Miss Erina!
Everything has been prepared
and is ready to go.
Very well. Let's do it.
You, do the best you can do
with your meager talents.
Don't embarrass yourself.
(Groaning)
Um... Are you
guys alright?
When it comes to it,
we'll show ya we got
what it takes!
C'mon, get up, Zenji!
We're all going to go back
to the dorm together!
Kyokusei! Let's Fight!
Yeaaaaah!
Y‐yeah!
[GIN]
Such a peaceful night...
It's quite a bit different
from the clamor of our
challenges all day long.
Perhaps, but I would say
at ze present time...
The students appear to be
in frantic disarray...
in a way that is far
beyond their habitual discord.
(Sigh)
[SCHOOLGIRL]
Is this going be enough?
Maybe we should try some
different seasonings?
This challenge is
a lot more harsh
than I expected.
Yeah, it is...
Unless you're really confident
in your cooking abilities,
you're not going to be
getting much sleep tonight.
I think I'm about
ready to go to bed.
You still tinkering
with your dish?
Um, yes. I'm still
just halfway done.
Okay then. Don't keep
at it too long.
That's Miss Erina,
all right.
It's like she doesn't feel
the pressure at all!
I can't help but admire
her regal attitude!
[ERINA]
Oh, also...
Tomorrow, we're
having a rematch.
In last night's game of Old
Maid...
You see, I wasn't really
feeling in my usual form.
You will be ready, right?
Yes, of course!
Oh, Miss Erina!
No matter what you do, you're
determined to be the victor.
Such an honorable soul!
Ahhhh!
Soma Yukihira...
I am going to crush you
into tiny little pieces,
you filthy peasant.
Keep your eyes open tomorrow.
You are getting a
first‐hand look at what it
takes to be Tohtsuki material.
A buffet is just an
all‐you‐can‐eat food bonanza.
Nothing's coming to mind for a
fancy hotel breakfast...
Guess I'll just
start making something!
The staples of egg cuisine...
In Japanese cooking,
it's rolled omelets.
And in Western cooking,
it's a scramble.
Woohoo!
It's tasty... Really tasty.
But it's still not enough.
[JOICHIRO](Laugh)
A new menu item, huh?
It's an interesting
dish, alright.
But it's just not right.
What? Why not?
I thought you said
you really liked it!
Listen to me, Soma:
Our food is more down‐to‐earth.
Customers come to Yukihira
for friendly conversation
and comfort food.
If we start serving a
bunch of fancy stuff,
it changes who we
are, understand?
I can't put out some dish
that's just there for
pure show..
I need an egg dish worthy
of a five‐star hotel...
Make a single dish,
one gives a sense of
wonder for the day.
I've gotta come up
with something,
an idea that has
something special about it...
That's it!
It's done!
Perfect! A breakfast using the
Aldini family techniques!
AHAHA!
Oh just you wait, Soma!
You shall witness my cooking!
Takumi, if you're done,
then why don't you go
to bed already?
(Megumi whimpers)
What should I do?
What should I do?!
I have to hurry and come
up with something!
Just make the kind of food
YOU would want to eat.
That'll be enough.
It's hospitality...
And it is the essence
of your cooking.
Some people don't eat
a lot in the mornings...
so maybe making a bunch of
food isn't the best way to go.
I have to think portions...
Okay then. I've got it!
Urrgh! I told you, dude!
Shut your face, bro!
(Snoring)
Ahh!
Hah! Hyaa!
Right, I've got the general
idea.
Now to give it a quick trial‐
Um, uh, hello there!
Who the heck
are you?
Hmm...
Seems like you'll be making
something pretty delicious.
Oh, you think so?
I hope to.
[SOMA]
What's with this girl?
Her skin and hair
are so pale...
(Chuckle)
I'm really looking forward
to tomorrow morning.
Well, I'll be
seeing you.
OW!
Oww...
What are you doing?!
Don't just stand there, MOVE IT!
But my lady, you told me to
stay back here and not move.
I told you to
do that when we're
intimidating someone!
But that part's over!
You're supposed to come
across all super‐menacing
lurking there behind me
with your eyeliner
and hair and stuff.
Hey! What happened to
your balls? You should
be playing with them.
Forgot to bring
'em with me. Sorry.
You've gotta
be kidding me!
I gave you
that awesome prop
so you'd look even
more weird and creepy!
You really don't
get it, do you?
Ah, my apologies.
What were we
talking about again?
We really weren't
talking about much...
In fact, I thought
you were leaving.
So have you guys already
decided what you'll be making?
Yeah, sorta.
Well, good luck with
your trial dish. See you.
Okay, that was
kinda strange.
So that was
Soma Yukihira.
After all the rumors,
he was kind of a letdown,
wasn't he?
I can't believe that's
what he plans to make.
(Giggle)
[ALICE]
You don't suppose
he wants to get
kicked out, do you?
Ohohohohoho...
AHAHAHA!
Uh! Huh? Whoa!
This place is huge!
Hey, wake up, man!
Oh, sorry about that.
Oh! Megumi's here too!
And she's over there doing
that crazy stuff again.
Takumi's here.
I think he's trying to
tell me something,
but he's so far I
can't make it out.
Oh well, looks like
this is my spot.
Hey, Erina!
Guess we're neighbors!
Soma Yukihira,
why are you here?!
We've seen a lot of each
other lately, haven't we?
This scumbag keeps popping up!
It's really getting
on my nerves.
This is my first time to witness
your famous cooking up close.
Still, I suppose this will be
a good chance to show him
what real cooking looks like.
By all means feel free
to have yourself a taste...
of the gap between
your cooking and mine!
Huh? You mean, we'll
taste and compare?
Sure, that's cool.
We'll do it
after the challenge.
Ah! Uh, no!
WE are not doing
anything, you got that?
This low‐life
just doesn't get it!
Well, best of luck
to you, Erina.
Ah! What do you
think you're doing?
You're, like, not planning
on making a souffle, are you?
Well kinda...
I'm going to be
making an omelet.
But I'll whisk the egg
whites into a meringue
before cooking them...
and that should give it a
different texture from just
your regular omelet.
It will be a souffle omelet.
Delivering
an unexpected texture...
Y'know, like what Chef Dojima
was talking about.
Uhh...
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
"Texture," huh? Hmph!
[GIN]
I assume you've finished
prepping for your dishes.
And I'm sure you'd like
to know the conditions
required for you to pass.
But first, allow me
to introduce your judges.
Huh?
Yay!
Oh crap! Kids!
[GIN]
Welcome our suppliers
and their families.
They provide the ingredients
used here at Tohtsuki Resort.
They serve as judges every
year,
and have also come up
with the theme, an egg
dish with a sense of wonder.
Uh. There's so
many of them!
These guys know their stuff
and they are very precise.
[TOKUZO] (Laughs)
Thanks for the
introduction.
Keep in mind,
we eat nothing that's
not up to our strict standards!
Hehehe.
Hm. Hm. Hm.
These old‐timers are... legit!
These guys look
like trouble.
They look pretty
dang serious!
[GIN]
Tohtsuki Resort's staff
from the cooking and service
divisions will also be
acting as your judges.
(Nervous gasps)
Wha‐?!
[AOKI]
That's the maitre d'
of the hotel!
[SATO]
No freakin' way!
Even Chef Dojima's
sous‐chef is here!
Two criteria
must be met:
First the producers
and staff must approve.
Second our guests must eat 200
of your plates in two hours.
Now remember, be vigilant
and keep your customers happy.
They are who
matter the most.
Two hundred plates, huh?
I see.
Women and men, young and old...
A diverse clientele.
They're totally simulating
an early breakfast rush.
This is the closest thing
they've done that's
anything like real cooking.
Whoever meets these
criteria shall pass!
Now then, judges in all
assembly halls
enjoy this breakfast to your
hearts' content!
[GIN]
Let the judgment begin!
Sorry for the wait!
Please! Come and get it!
Please! Over here!
Feel free to
help yourself!
What a rich and
flavorful aroma...
What is it?
A frittata.
[WAITRESS 1]
That's an Italian
egg dish, right?
You fold cheese into
the eggs and cook them.
Yeah, sorry, but it kinda
seems a little ordinary
if you ask me...
[TAKUMI]
Not at all.
My frittata is meant to be
broken into rough chunks
and sprinkled onto
a bed of salad,
where it will be gently
tossed to merge flavors.
Next, it's drizzled with
balsamic vinegar and topped
with grated parmesan cheese.
And it's done!
An insalata di frittata!
That looks really good.
So we're talking about
a "salad," then.
Ahh! This is so good!
The combination of fluffy eggs
and fresh crisp vegetables
is so unexpected...
When you take a bite, it
blends all in with this
refreshing sauce!
Incredible! I've never
had a salad like this before!
Grazie!
Um... Hello?
HM!
Please have some,
if you like!
I would be honored!
I call it "Single‐size
morning stew"!
For breakfast? A stew?!
What is this you've put at
the end of each of our skewers?
[KOSUKE]
She's included a
quail egg on here!
Hmm!
M'kay. I see.
Chicken eggs aren't the
only kind of breakfast.
Not a bad little idea.
Ooooh! Goodness gracious!
This taste is so soothing.
Each bite exudes the
mellow flavor of the base!
These vegetables were
chosen to match the
size of the quail egg
and are quite colorful...
You can't help but reach for
the next bite!
HMM!
AAHHH!
Would you...
please marry my grandson?
Huh?!
Um, well...
WHA‐?!
[SCHOOLBOY]
Welcome!
Oh! This is interesting.
A loco moco on a
buffet line.
Guh!
It's standard to top a loco
moco with gravy,
but this is a vinaigrette!
The refreshing acidity
of the white wine vinegar
elevates the egg yolk's
runniness and the juiciness
of the meat!
Incredible...
It's brimming with exuberance!
She really pulled it off!
Okay! I was able to
make use of a new dish
I created at Bowl‐club.
I oughta get to
200 servings in no time.
Hey... Don't I recognize
you from somewhere?
I, uh...
Oh. You were
one of Erina's
underlings, right?
Oh wow!
I haven't seen you
around that much lately.
[ALICE]
I think I get it.
She left you twisting in
the wind, didn't she?
Are you looking to get your
ass kicked or somethin'?
Oops! Sorry if
that's a sore spot.
Grrrr...
[IKUMI]
Wait. What's the
deal with her dish?
She's got a fried egg,
a boiled egg still
in the shell,
and an egg cut in two?
Not a lot of effort,
if you ask me.
She's not getting any
customers at all.
Just what is she thinking?
Good morning.
I'm serving Eggs Benedict.
Whoa! Those look
really beautiful!
[WAITER 2]
They're like dazzling jewels!
Alright, so Eggs Benedict...
A poached egg and bacon
are set atop an english muffin
and covered with a tangy
hollandaise sauce.
Americans eat these all the
time with Canadian bacon...
Well it's not exactly what
I would call "new."
I'm not expecting a lot
of "wonder" from this.
The poached egg is
cooked perfectly and
melts on the tongue.
The hollandaise sauce has
just the right acidity.
The bacon is perfectly
crisp and the muffin has
a faint sweetness.
These flavors all blend
together, enveloping the
tongue...
No! That's not all!
Ah! This powder, sparkling
amidst the egg's golden yolk...
It's mullet roe!
She coated the muffin with
powdered mullet roe?!
That's brilliant!
It's another type of egg!
The sublime saltiness of the
roe pairs with the egg yolks,
creating a huge
depth of flavor!
The Queen of Breakfast...
She was given that nickname
at a famous,
established shop
in New York.
And this dish is
truly of royal caliber!
This culinary masterwork will
make you bow before it!
Yeah, well that's the point.
(Ending Song Begins)
[WAITRESS 1]
How gorgeous!
[WAITRESS 2]
I can't even stand it!
[WAITER]
Miss Erina!
[GROUP]
The Queen of Eggs Benedict!
[GIN]
Erina Nakiri!
You have served two hundred!
Huh? It's alright, I'll
catch up soon enough!
How's Soma doing?!
I'm halfway there.
What about Soma?
What's going on?
Huh?! Soma!
Are you kidding me?!
He's only served 10 people?!
(Shaky inhale)
[GIRLS]
Next time on Food Wars,
it's the fourteenth course...
[IKUMI]
All hell's breaking loose!
[GIRLS]
"Metamorphose"
[RYOKO]
I am going to ferment! Woohoo!
[ISSHIKI]
I will NOT give up the top
spot at Kyokusei!
Never!