[theme music]
-The spiderwebs which entangled
you have now been severed.
Use that bow to
save the priestess.
-Kagome!
Where are you?
What?
Kagome!
Are you OK?
Wake up.
-(VOICEOVER) That Kikyo
was only an illusion.
Something created
by my own heart.
All that time, I was
fighting against a phantom.
-You did it.
You brought back the bow.
-Inuyasha.
Is that really you?
-It's me.
Are you OK?
-Yeah.
He came for me.
In the sky!
Those are Naraku's spider webs.
-Something's coming.
-Run, quickly.
-Kikyo.
-Koga.
You must run.
-I can't do that.
I just picked up Naraku's scent.
He's somewhere nearby, isn't he?
-(VOICEOVER) Don't
you understand?
Naraku is already here.
-Huh?
Lady Kikyo!
Huh?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Among the Twinkling Stars.
-They're gone.
-Naraku.
KIKYO: Koga.
Why didn't you run?
-What's the matter now?
Besides, isn't this
what you wanted?
You the one who's been trying
to give Naraku my jewel shards.
I wouldn't even be
here if you hadn't
been using Midoriko's
soul to mess with my legs.
-The situation has changed.
I can no longer help.
-The webs have loosened!
-We're falling!
-Kirara!
-What?
-Kikyo.
So, how does it feel
to know you shall
die in the arms of your
most hated enemy?
-There you are, you coward.
-Naraku!
-You wanted me?
Well, here I am!
Goraishi!
-How amusing.
-Please, save your
strength, Koga.
If your Shikon jewel
shards are taken,
we will be powerless
against him!
-Don't you worry.
I've got this.
-You cannot evade me forever.
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): His shards.
The jewel shards in Koga's
legs are being purified.
It can only be the will
of Midoriko's soul.
If Naraku were to
consume those shards,
they would purify the jewel.
It would destroy him!
Naraku hasn't noticed them yet.
-This must be difficult
for you, seeing
me collect the final
shards, knowing
there is nothing you can do
to stop me from completing it.
-You can say whatever you want.
When Inuyasha arrives,
none of it will matter.
-What?
-Goraishi!
-Hm.
-Inuyasha.
On the mountain, I was tested
by an illusion of Kikyo.
-An illusion of Kikyo?
-Yeah.
It was an illusion
created by my heart.
A really scary and
hateful version of Kikyo.
The weird thing is,
that's how she was before.
I remember she hated me, and
she even tried to kill you.
-It's true.
But Kikyo isn't
like that anymore.
-No.
She's not.
But it made me
realize part of me
must still see her
like that, and it
makes me feel, well, ashamed.
INUYASHA: Don't
beat yourself up.
-Huh?
-I mean, it didn't stop you from
wanting to save Kikyo, right?
If that's not proof
that your heart's pure,
I don't know what is.
-(VOICEOVER) I hope
you're right about that.
-Hang on.
I'm getting worried
about scrawny wolf boy.
-Koga!
-His miasma.
It's happening again.
My lips won't move.
-You're mine.
-(VOICEOVER) That's
right, Naraku.
Now just make contact
with Koga's shards.
You and I are
connected by your web.
That means once you touch
the shards, both of us
will be purified.
Than I can join
Midoriko in destroying
you once and for all.
I may even be able
to save Koga's life.
-Damn it!
-(VOICEOVER) Naraku.
I will not die here.
You hear me?
I will not allow myself to
die in your filthy arms!
Inuyasha.
-Lady Kikyo!
-No!
-Kikyo.
As long as my spider
web connects us,
there can be no secrets.
I am well aware of the
hatred and contempt
you feel towards
me, not to mention
your lingering
affection for Inuyasha.
Oh.
Isn't it a pity, Kikyo?
Dying in the arms
of your hated enemy.
Knowing that you
will never again see
your beloved Inuyasha.
INUYASHA: Naraku!
You let her go!
-Inuyasha.
-Kikyo!
I only have one arrow.
I can't afford to miss.
-There is only one way.
You must shoot my
wound using this bow.
Only that can purify
Naraku's contamination.
-(VOICEOVER) It's OK.
I'll show them.
I'll hit it!
-Wait.
-What?
You don't want me to shoot yet?
-Kagome!
Kagome.
-Koga.
You're OK!
-Yeah.
Ha got a hold of me,
but I managed to escape.
-Huh?
The shards in his legs
have been purified.
-Naraku.
I'm gonna make you pay for this!
-You must be happy, Kikyo.
Your beloved Inuyasha
has arrived just in time
to watch you die.
-That's not gonna happen.
Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga!
-He regenerated.
-But he cut through
his demon vortex!
-Now you see.
That sword of yours
will never beat--
-What is that?
-The inside of Narake's body.
-The Dragon Scale
Tetsusaiga must have worked.
-That and Koga's jewel shards.
KAGOME: I see it.
The Shikon jewel.
Inuyasha!
The Shikon jewel
is inside his body!
-Good.
I'll cut through
you and the jewel!
Kikyo!
Kikyo.
Hang in there, Kikyo.
-His body's closing up!
-Koga, wait!
-My jewel shards are supposed
to purify Naraku, aren't they?
Well, it's now or never.
Let's see if it works.
I wasn't planning to play
along with Midoriko's soul,
but what choice have I got.
-If he makes it inside, Naraku
and the jewel will be purified.
-The jewel's presence is gone.
It's a trap!
Naraku doesn't have the jewel!
-What?
-No!
Koga!
Don't go in there!
It's a trap!
He doesn't have it!
-What?
-Ha.
Too late now.
-I don't understand.
Where it go?
-I don't know.
One minute, the jewel was
there, and the next it was gone.
It just disappeared.
-In that case, we can't allow
Koga to enter Naraku's body.
-Instead of purifying Naraku,
the shards in his legs
will be instantly defiled.
There isn't much time left.
Sango, let's go.
-Kikyo.
Come on, Kikyo.
-Inuyasha?
-Kikyo.
Go.
Go save Koga.
-But--
-Go.
Hurry.
-Don't worry.
I'll be back for you, OK?
-I'll rip you apart from inside!
[laughter]
-This is the end, Koga.
Huh?
-Sango, I won't be able
to do this without you.
-You can't.
It's too dangerous.
-You will gain nothing.
Your body it will
infected by miasma,
and you shall suffer
a painful death long
before you suck me
into your Wind Tunnel.
-We'll see about that.
Wind Tunnel!
-Miroku!
-Come on!
Just a little bit longer!
-Poo fool.
The only thing you're
sucking in is miasma.
-That's all I need!
-What?
-The miasma's gone.
Now's my chance!
Goraishi!
-Are you OK?
-I'll take it from here, Miroku!
-(VOICEOVER) The
wound is spreading.
-Miroku, are you all right?
-Yes.
-You alive, wolf boy?
-Are you kidding?
I barely got a scratch.
-Then hurry up and-- huh?
Koga?
-Koga's Shikon jewel
shards have darkened.
We have to hurry.
Where-- where is Naraku
hiding the Shikon jewel?
My power isn't strong
enough to locate it.
Where is it, Kikyo?
Huh?
Is that what I think it is?
All this time, Naraku had the
jewel hidden inside Kikyo?
-Those are Kikyo's
soul collectors.
-(VOICEOVER) Now.
-Now?
You want me to shoot?
I'll shoot now.
-What's this?
So you've found the
jewel, have you?
-Kagome!
-Thank you, soul collectors.
-Damn you.
-He's trying to take
back the Shikon jewel.
I won't let that happen.
-Now I see.
You wish to purify
me and the jewel.
-Go!
-Huh?
The cloud of miasma's
defiling the jewel!
-Watch me consume it.
What?
-Kikyo's spiritual energy
is destroying Naraku!
-They're coming loose!
-My Shikon jewel shards!
-Who cares about that right now?
[scream]
-(VOICEOVER) Kikyo's spiritual
energy is fighting against
Naraku's demonic energy.
Can you see it, Kikyo?
Naraku's in pain right now.
-Kagome.
The rest is up to you.
-What?
His demonic energy's
overcoming it.
[laughter]
-I've won.
[gasp]
KIKYO: Kagome.
-Hm?
-Protect the last shard.
Protect Kohaku's light.
This is something
only you can do now.
-You can't mean that!
You'll be OK!
And I couldn't
possibly-- Kikyo--
but I shot you with the bow,
just like you wanted me to.
It should have
purified the wound.
[laughter]
-Kikyo, it appears you've lost.
-(VOICEOVER) We
shall see, Naraku.
You'll only know whether I've
truly lost or not when you die.
-Not so fast, Naraku.
-Only one shard left,
and no one to stop me.
We'll see how courageous you are
without Kikyo protecting you.
-Huh?
Kikyo!
-That's right.
She's finished.
She lost to my demonic energy.
KAGOME: Inuyasha!
Hurry!
It's Kikyo!
-Kikyo--
RIN: Come back, Kohaku!
You're not supposed to move!
-I must return.
Lady Kikyo is in danger.
I have to go and find her.
-Just to be clear, don't
expect Lord Sesshomaru
to bring you along with us!
-Couldn't we at least ask him?
SESSHOMARU: The scent
in the wind has changed.
-Huh?
Does that means something's
happened to Lady Kikyo?
-It's too late.
KAEDE: All right, children.
It's time to head back inside.
-OK.
-Wow, the sunset looks so red.
Isn't it pretty, Lady Kaede?
-Yes.
(VOICEOVER) A deep red.
Practically the color of blood.
-Is she--
-Kikyo-- I tried, but
I couldn't save her.
-Please, I'd like to
be alone with her.
-(VOICEOVER) I'm sorry, Kikyo.
I'm so sorry!
KIKYO (VOICEOVER):
Don't cry, Kagome.
My soul was saved.
I can die in peace.
-Huh?
Those are-- my sister's
KIKYO (VOICEOVER):
Forgive me, Kaede.
-Big sister.
-It must not have been easy.
I know you have suffered
greatly because of me, sister.
-That's not true.
-Forgive me, Kaede.
-Kikyo!
-I had the chance
to destroy Naraku.
If I had done it,
then things wouldn't
have ended up this way.
-Miroku--
-But I didn't do it.
I was so afraid for
my own life that I
hesitated to open
the Wind Tunnel.
That woman saved my life.
She needed my help, and I just--
-That's not true.
I think Kikyo knew what
was going to happen,
and she wanted you to
survive for my sake.
-Sango--
SANGO: I thought
I despised Kikyo.
All I knew was that she
was willing to sacrifice
my brother and his
shard to defeat Naraku.
His life didn't seem
to matter to her.
However, when I saw
her try to save Koga,
I realized I was
wrong about her.
Kikyo was fighting to
protect Kohaku's life.
She'd been trying to
protect all of us.
-(VOICEOVER) Well, my
jewel shards are gone.
But I'm still alive.
Was that your plan
for me, Kikyo?
-It didn't work.
I thought I could save her,
but I couldn't do anything.
It took me too long.
I had too much doubt.
I couldn't get back
in time to save her.
Poor Kikyo.
-Damn that Naraku.
He kept telling her that she
would never see Inuyasha again.
But he made it in time.
-It's been so long.
-Huh?
-Do you remember
those days, Inuyasha?
When we were happy?
Long before Naraku
tore us apart.
Inuyasha, would you
be willing to use
the Shikon jewel
to become a human?
-Well, if I were to
become a human, what
would you do, Kikyo?
-I am the guardian
of the Shikon jewel.
But if it did not exist,
I'd be an ordinary woman.
-How could I forget?
-Back then, I want
to become human.
So we could spend
our lives together.
-At last, I have become
an ordinary woman.
-Kikyo, you were the first
woman that I ever loved.
The first person that
I ever cared for.
But I-- I still
couldn't save you.
-You've ne And that, Inuyasha.
I think that's the first
time I've ever seen you cry.
-Kikyo, I'm sorry.
You needed me, and
I couldn't save you.
-It doesn't matter.
You came for me.
That was enough.
-Kikyo--
-Inuyasha.
-Kikyo.
-Look at this light.
-It's Kikyo's soul.
-It almost feels as if
she's saying goodbye.
-It's so warm.
Inuyasha?
-Kikyo doesn't want
us to mourn her.
She says she'll
protect us forever.
[theme music]
KAGOME: Koga heads home
for some much needed rest,
and Sesshomaru makes an
unexpected trip of his own.
-If you've come to
visit your mother,
I can only assume you have
questions about the Tenseiga.
SESSHOMARU: You must
have heard from father
how to use Tenseiga to
perform Meido Zangetsuha.
-Very well, then.
I shall have you entertain me.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"Inuyasha, The Final Act."
Sesshomaru in the Underworld.
-Sacrifices are
inevitable if one
wishes to be well versed
in the art of the sword.