[theme music]
-Flowers wither and
lose their color.
Much as I reflect in vain
time lost to the long rain.
Kagura.
Are you free now?
Did you ever become the wind?
I-- I have nothing.
I have nothing.
-Go!
-What?
It's still there.
One speck of purity
within the Shikon jewel.
Despite my efforts to defile
it, the stubborn point of light
remains.
And our last battle
powered Inuyasha's blade.
It could still cost me my life.
Kikyo.
Even in death you
continue to haunt me.
Damn you.
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
Flowers Drenched in Sadness.
-Ah.
The sun's coming out.
Shall we take a short break?
-Why don't you
suck it up, Miroku?
You know we don't
have time to spare.
-Inuyasha, you really are
a fool, you know that?
He was suggesting we take a rest
for your sake, not his, dummy.
-For my sake?
Why me?
-Because you're ah-- ah choo.
-Oh.
-Smells great.
A little village.
The smell.
There's something
soothing about it.
-Soothing?
More like sickening.
It's making me
dizzy, it's so sweet.
-Ah choo!
-Wow, Shippo.
Are you OK?
-Can't stop sneezing.
[sneezing]
-Kirara.
You too, huh?
-Hope you don't have far to go.
It'll be dusk soon.
-You're welcome to
stay if you'd like.
We could put you
up for the night.
-We'd love to.
-That's very kind of you.
-Choo!
-That's it?
No discussion?
Just like that, we're staying?
-Your village is so lovely with
all these flowers everywhere.
-Yes, isn't peaceful?
-I'm exhausted.
-Don't you walk away from me.
MIROKU: Hurry up, Inuyasha.
-This house was built especially
for travelers like you to use.
Please.
Make yourselves at home.
We'll see you in the morning.
-Yes.
Enjoy your stay.
-You're all so careless.
-Look.
You need rest more
than any of us.
-Ha.
What do you know?
Sitting around just
makes it worse.
-Sheesh.
He mever stops complaining.
Kagome, please tell him to sit.
-Hmph.
-What's the point?
He can't help it.
It's obvious
Inuyasha still hasn't
gotten over Kikyo's death.
MAN: Esteemed
Flower Prince, sir.
You'll be pleased
to know that we
have new travelers
staying the night.
-Oh?
You're right, that
does please me.
Ah, the scent of
an injured soul.
This fragrance.
I never tire of it.
[sneezing]
-(VOICEOVER) The scent of those
flowers is getting stronger.
Damn it.
I can't stand this sweet smell.
The stronger it gets,
the more uneasy I feel.
KAGOME: Inuyasha.
-Huh?
-You should try
to get some rest.
I know you're tired.
You haven't been sleeping much.
Not since the day Kikyo died.
-Don't worry about it.
I'll be fine.
-You can't sleep?
-Of course I can.
I just don't want to.
If I fall asleep,
I'll dream about ehr.
About Kikyo.
-Ah-- Ah-- Ah choo!
-Shippo.
Poor thing.
You're all stuffed up.
You should probably
blow your nose.
-Sorry if I woke you up.
I wonder what this is.
My eyes are itchy too.
-It's gotta be all
these stupid flowers.
-You mean allergies?
-Aller-what?
-I knew something wasn't
right about this village.
I mean, why would they build
a house just for travelers?
It's not like they're
that well off.
It's weird.
-I guess.
It's kind of weird.
-Sh.
-Are those the villagers?
-Yeah.
Something's definitely wrong.
-It's so soothing.
-Yes.
The flowers soothe my soul.
-I'm so happy.
-My soul is at peace.
-(VOICEOVER) What's
happening to them?
It looks serious.
-Indeed, we cannot
afford to ignore this.
-What do we do?
-Wake up!
-Are you OK?
-I don't think so.
-They all turned into soil.
-They'll be perfect
for my flowers.
Look around.
Flowers thrive in happy
soil, don't you find?
-Who the hell are you?
-Flower Prince, sir.
-Flower Prince?
-My dear villagers,
you seem upset.
I imagine you must be
quite disappointed.
-Yes, we are, because we
were unable to become soil.
-Bastard.
What have you done
to all these people?
-Now, now.
I simply offered the villagers a
chance a peace and tranquility.
-Everyone.
Don't breathe it in.
-I've missed you, sister.
-Kohaku?
-Sango.
-The poor girl.
Worrying about the
fate of her brother
has obviously driven
her to madness.
Perhaps I can ease
her pain, though.
-(VOICEOVER) How does
he know about Kohaku?
-You.
How were you able to
read Sango's mind?
-You are haunted
by injury, a wound
you sustained that
threatens your life.
Not that I blame you.
All men fear death.
-(VOICEOVER) He even
knows about my injuries.
How is he doing it?
-You don't have
to worry anymore.
Resign yourselves
to the flowers.
It will bring you the
joy and everlasting piece
that has so long eluded you.
-I've heard enough of this.
Wind Scar!
Huh?
He's gone?
-Is that his blood?
-You must've wounded him.
-I'm gonna follow his trail.
The rest of you, stay here.
-I'm coming with you.
-Thanks anyway, but I can deal
with this freak by myself.
-Be careful.
It might not be as
easy as you think.
-She's right, Inuyasha.
The Flower Prince seems to feast
on people's sorrow and pain,
and you've got
both in abundance.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not as delicate as
the rest of you people.
-Wait!
Inuyasha!
-Lady Kagome.
Take these.
Beads of demon repulsion.
-Thanks Miroku.
Stay here and look after
Sango and the villagers.
-Hello?
Where did-- Ah choo!
--everyone go?
-This is rough, huh Kirara?
-(VOICEOVER) I'm glad we're
not just sitting around.
I'd rather be fighting.
At least then I don't have
to think about anything.
Like Kikyo.
-(VOICEOVER) Farewell, Kagura.
-Hello, Kanna.
I bring a message for Naraku.
He wishes for you to lure
Inuyasha and his friends
in and unleash the mirror.
KAGOME: Is that the place?
INUYASHA: Yesh.
There's no mistake.
FLOWER PRINCE: Welcome
to my humble abode.
-Bastard.
-Oh.
If you've come to apologize
for your violent behavior,
there's no need.
-Ha.
Not a chance.
It hardly matters.
As you can see, I
wasn't actually injured.
And as for the blood,
well, that was merely
a personal invitation
to my home.
-So, you think you fooled us?
-I have little doubt your
soul will taste exquisite.
I prefer to devour it here
where I can truly savor it.
-What the--
-They're turning red!
-(VOICEOVER) Dammit.
I can't move.
-I've studied tou,
and I can tell
that your soul is in
a very fragile state.
I can feel your pain through
the vines and the pollen.
I see you've suffered
a great loss.
The woman you love most in this
world has died, hasn't she?
You must be sad.
Sad enough to follow her into
death, and beyond, perhaps?
-Shut your mouth!
-Come, and I shall
set your mind at ease.
-Inuyasha!
Inuyasha.
He's gone too.
The beads of demon repulsion.
I see.
They prevent the flowers
from invading my soul.
I guess that's why
I still feel sad.
-Is it you?
-I knew you'd come, Inuyasha.
-Kikyo.
-You're hopeless.
You know that?
-Kikyo-- huh?
Kikyo!
-Inuyasha, let's go.
Together.
FLOWER PRINCE: Your face
looks so peaceful now.
I see you've suffered
a great lost.
The woman you love most in this
world has died, hasn't she?
You must be sad.
Sad enough to follow her into
death, and beyond, perhaps.
-(VOICEOVER) You can't
want to follow her.
You can't, Inuyasha.
Inuyasha!
Where are you?
Ah!
-There's no sense
in fighting it.
Go ahead and cry if you want.
[gasp]
-Inuyasha!
I know you're in there!
Inuyasha!
-It's too late.
For the heart of this man
is no longer in this world.
-(VOICEOVER) Kagome.
-But why?
You-- you were finally at peace.
Why would you give that up?
-You talk way too much.
Shut it!
-I merely showed you the
dreams you wished to see.
I shall rip your heart
out for defying me!
-(VOICEOVER) I have to
break through this barrier.
Before it's too late!
Please let this work.
-Kagome's arrow?
Kagome, where are you?
Kagome.
Kagome, hang in there.
FLOWER PRINCE: What a surprise.
Huh?
FLOWER PRINCE: The girl's
soul has a delectable taste.
More appealing than yours.
-I thought I killed you!
FLOWER PRINCE: Indeed, that girl
is hurting more than you are.
-What?
FLOWER PRINCE:
It's plain to see,
the source of this
girl's sorrow is--
-Why so quiet?
I know why.
You just figured out
what was on my mind.
Isn't that right?
-Kagome--
-In that case, you
know what comes next.
Take this!
-Damn you!
-Huh?
-Is it amusing for you
to look into the hearts
of other people?
Remind them of their pain?
Well, the pain I feel
isn't for you to consume.
You won't get so
much as a taste.
You hear me?
-You get 'em?
-No.
Not yet.
There are still flowers left.
Go hide.
You're the one he wants now.
Wait.
Don't move, Kagome!
Take that!
[gasp]
[sneeze]
MIROKU: The flowers.
SANGO: They're disappearing.
-Yeah, and my eyes
have stopped itching.
-Kagome, are you OK?
-Fine.
How about you?
Thanks to you.
-(VOICEOVER) He
wept tears of blood.
Whatever happened, it must
have been hard for him.
-Before you came, I had
a dream about Kikyo.
-Oh?
-When I saw her, she
asked me to go with her.
-Did you want to?
-I never answered.
you woke me up.
-(VOICEOVER) That doesn't
answer my question.
-I couldn't save Kikyo's life.
And that caused
me a lot of pain.
For some reason, I
didn't want help.
I thought it was something
I had to go through alone.
I guess I was so focused
on my own suffering,
I couldn't see yours.
I never realized that you
were in pain, just like me.
Forgive me, Kagome.
-OK.
I'm just glad you came back.
The thing is, Kikyo's death
was hard for all of us.
But I know that it must have
been especially hard on you.
I understand.
It'll all be OK.
-Kagome-- you-- I don't get it.
How are you so strong?
-I am not strong, you idiot!
-Ah!
-You should be asking,
are you so kind?
I'm kind.
-Right.
You're kind.
Very kind.
-(VOICEOVER) He
might be cluseless,
but I'm still glad he came back.
-It doesn't make sense.
How come only Kirara
and I had to deal
with sneezing and the sniffles?
-Let me see.
Maybe it's because you
don't have a single worry
in the world, just like Kirara.
-Maybe Shippo's just trying
to help us his own way.
-Yeah, that's right.
Since you're always so gloomy.
-Sorry I'm not a
ray of sunshine.
-Naraku, it would apear
that our troublesome friends
are on the move yet again.
[laughter]
MIROKU: A strange
light, you say?
-Yes.
We noticed it last night.
-The mountains were lit
up as if it were daylight.
It was very unnatural.
-I wish we could tell
you more, but none of us
dares go near it.
-I think I see it.
-Yes.
It looks to be coming from
somewhere near the lake.
-This is kind of
weird, isn't it?
-Why's that?
-Well, as far as I
remember, you never
liked helping out strangers.
But you agreed to help them
without a second though?
-So?
I can't help people out now?
-He gets anxious if he
doesn't do anything.
He needs to do this.
-I am not anxious.
I don't get anxious.
-Sure, sure.
Of course you're not.
-(VOICEOVER) Besides.
Even though it's faint, this
is definitely Naraku's scent.
-What happened here?
-The lake water has been
transformed into a mirror.
-Kagome, there's something
in the middle of the lake.
-You're right.
It's Kanna's mirror.
-It's a mirror demon.
-I was waiting for this.
-Kanna.
This must be another
one of Naraku's traps!
-So bright!
-That's pathetic.
Were you hoping
that would blind us?
-What is that?
Tetsusaiga?
-(VOICEOVER) Why does that
thing have Tetsusaiga?
In his hand?
-Careful.
That's no reflection.
It seems that Kanna's
mirror has actually
transformed into a demon.
It may have all the
powers of your Tetsusaiga.
-It's just a trick
of the mirror.
A phantom reflection.
Nothing more!
You're not fooling me, Kanna.
Now take this.
Wind Scar!
-His Wind Scar isn't working!
-(VOICEOVER) So it didn't
just copy the shape?
It also stole the
demonic energy?
-Your turn.
Wind Scar.
-It's real!
Get out of here.
You're too slow.
Adamant Barrage!
That doesn't work either?
-Inuyasha.
I suggest we pull back now.
-Hurry up, before
the Adamant Barrage!
-Adamant Barrage.
-Dammit.
-Fox Magic!
-A flower.
Flowers wither and
lose their color.
Much as I reflect in vain
time lost to the long rain.
[theme music]
KAGOME: Naraku intends
for Kanna and Inuyasha
to kill each other.
-Don't let up, Kanna.
Continue until there's
nothing left of Tetsusaiga.
Know that this is the very
purpose of your existence.
-There's a light within
the defiled Shikon jewel.
Kanna, are you the one
showing this to me?
INUYASHA: Next time on
"Inuyasha, The Final Act."
Kanna's Gravestone.
-The light.
The light will destroy Naraku.