[theme music]
-I know why you've come.
-I'm here because I want
you to use my shard.
-Is that so?
I'm aware that you've
been following me
for quite some time.
Do you understand what it
will mean if I use your shard?
Do you realize what
will happen to you?
-I understand.
I'm willing to
sacrifice my life.
-Am I to believe, then,
that you do not fear death?
-I do not.
-(VOICEOVER) His
eyes show no fear.
Not even the
slightest hesitation.
Is life so painful for you
that you welcome death?
It saddens me greatly
to think that if we
had met under different
circumstances,
my only instinct would have
been to heal this child's
broken soul and encourage
him to live his life.
But my duty now forbids me
from doing that for him.
Forgive me, Kohaku.
-You're leaving us behind?
After all we've
been through, Koga?
-You're wasting your breath.
My mind's already made up.
I'm going after
Naraku on my own.
These Shikon jewel shards have
gotten the whole wolf demon
tribe involved now.
Plus, I don't know when my
legs will stop moving again
because of Midoriko's will.
It's nothing personal.
It's just too dangerous
for you to be around me.
Besides, you'd
only get in my way.
-That's it!
You can't do
anything without us!
-He's right!
You'll never make it without us.
-Wow.
You actually believe
that, don't you?
-Wait a sec, Koga.
-Look.
Both of us are after
the same thing,
so you know we'll be
crossing paths again.
You better not try to beat me
to the punch, scrawny, wolf boy.
-In that case, you better learn
to use that sword of yours.
-Yeah, yeah, you smart ass.
I know it won't be easy, Kagome,
but I'll be back for you.
See you.
-Bye you guys.
Thanks for helping us!
-You take care, little lady!
Until next time!
-You too!
Take care of yourselves!
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER) The
Great Holy Demon Spirit's Test.
-You ready, Kinka?
Today I shatter that skull
of yours once and for all.
-Silence, Ginka!
I'm gonna burn you alive
before you get the chance!
-Moryomaru.
Kinka and Ginka are forever
bound to one another.
You must obtain the power
of this bond between them.
Do that, and you
shall strengthen
the bond between you
and your new shell.
Consume them.
-Come on, boy.
Out with it.
What did he do this time?
-No, it's Tetsusaiga.
It hurt Inuyasha.
It tried to burn him.
I've never seen
anything like it.
-Oh, hello again, Totosai.
-Hm.
Here, let me have a look.
I see it's now capable of
absorbing demonic energy.
So?
-So I'm asking you what
the problem is, old man.
-There is nothing
wrong with Tetsusaiga.
If there's a problem, the
problem is you, Inuyasha.
-What are you talking about?
-Listen carefully.
Demonic energy is like
a poison of sorts.
Originally,
Tetsusaiga was forged
from the fang of your father,
who was a mighty demon.
He had the capacity to
absorb an infinite amount
of demonic energy.
However, you, who
are half human,
simply do not possess
the power to restrain
the demonic energy
absorbed by your own sword.
Now then.
Show me your hands.
-Ha.
What are you, gonna ready
my fortune or something?
-(VOICEOVER) Stubborn boy.
This much damage and you still
refuse to let go of the sword?
-The Dragon Scale
Tetsusaiga grew hotter
as it absorbed more
demonic energy.
-It was warning you of
the danger you faced.
A warning you would
have been wise to heed!
-(VOICEOVER) So Tetsusaiga
never wanted to hurt Inuyasha.
-All right.
What should I do?
-Now that Tetsusaiga
has become stronger,
you too must become
stronger to handle it.
-But how?
-It's going to take
extensive training.
-We don't have time for any
of that, and you know it.
-That is unfortunate,
but it's your fault
for ignoring my warning
in the first place.
-My fault?
I'm begging you for help,
and that's all you can say?
-Well, if this is
your idea of begging,
I'd have to see what
demanding looks like.
Since you insist, go meet
the great holy spirit!
-Holy demon spirit?
-He's the demon equivalent
of a wise old hermit.
If you want to master the
Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga,
you have no choice but
to go train under him.
-My turn!
What's this?
-Who dares to interfere
in our battle?
-(VOICEOVER) A few drops of
their blood are this effective?
Oh, I'll make good
use of you two.
I'm going to devour you both.
-You have wounded our body.
-You're going to regret it!
-Where is it?
-You idiot!
-What's this?
-Now, it's only a matter
of time before one of us
takes over your body.
-It is laughable
that a creature like
you would attempt to consume us.
-That armor of yours
won't protect you either.
-As we speak, fire and lightning
are penetrating your body.
You shall burn from
the inside out!
-Interesting.
If things continue this
way, even Naraku's heart
will be in danger.
You could at least
introduce yourself
before trying to kill me.
-I can smell Naraku's
scent on you.
That is all the reason I need.
-Is that so?
You must be Lord Sesshomaru.
-Tell me what Moryomaru
is doing here.
-Alas, I am but a
distant spectator.
-Kinka wasn't able
to break free.
Now's my chance to kill you!
-Ginka, you coward!
-You made it easy for me.
-Bastard.
-It was Ginka who chose
this fate for you,
not I. He could
have easily escaped,
but instead, he
chose to attack you.
-Shut up!
-You're no threat to me anymore.
-He was after the
power that connects
Kinka and Ginka's
demonic energy.
Not a bad acquisition.
Naraku might get more than he
bargained for with this one.
Huh?
Lord Sesshomaru?
-Sesshomaru.
-Moryomaru.
Why not test your newly acquired
power on me, if you're able to.
-I can see you've
got a new blade,
and I bet you're just itching
to try it out, aren't you?
As you wish!
-Meido Zangetsuha!
He's fleeing?
-It's nothing personal.
Naraku ordered me to
let him escape, you see.
Farewell, Lord Sesshomaru.
-If he's a hermit,
why live here?
-Good point.
It isn't very hermit-like.
-Hey.
Are you sure this
is the right way?
-Here?
MAN: Help!
Somebody help me!
-What?
-Now, this is what I'd expect
the residence of a demon hermit
to look like.
-Where was that
voice coming from?
MAN: Hey!
I'm over here!
You must help me
before I blow away.
-Is it laundry?
-No.
Laundry cannot speak.
-I do't suppose
that's the hermit?
-I think it might be.
-Thanks.
The wind was picking up.
So you're Inuyasha, are you?
I shall train you well, my boy.
At least that's what
I'd like to say, but--
-What?
-I can't.
Please leave.
-Bastard!
Why not?
Tell me!
-Sit, boy!
So, why can't you?
-Well, it happened last night.
I was preparing for
my evening meditation
when a demon attacked
me from behind,
and made off with all
my internal organs.
That's how I eneded
up like this.
-I see.
In that case, let us help you.
We just have to recover
your internal organs, right?
-No way!
I didn't sign up for that.
-It's a very nice though,
but this is not an opponent
that a half demon and a
bunch of humans can handle.
-Well, excuse me for only being
a half demon, oh wise one.
-You are not helping things.
-What is it, Kirara?
-Huh?
-This place is
crawling with demons!
-I'll cut every single
one of 'em down!
-Somebody stop that fool.
-Huh?
Sit, boy!
-What was that for?
-Isn't it obvious, boy?
Those aren't demons.
They're villagers.
-What?
-Their appearance has been
altered by demonic magic.
The demonic energy
drifting in the air
is from my missing organs.
-I thought the demon took them.
-While it absorbs the
energy, the demon can't move.
It is likely still in
the village somewhere.
-So it transformed the
villagers' appearance
to make htem look like demons
in order to hide amongst them.
-It requires less effort to
blend in than it does to hide.
-Look, If that's true, it
means that there's a real demon
somewhere nearby, right?
It seems simple to me.
We just have to find the demon
and get your organs back.
-What you're saying
makes a lot of sense.
-Huh?
-You bastard!
What the hell did
you do to my sword?
-It's a precaution.
I can't let you go around
attacking people at random.
-Hold it right there!
-Are you speaking to us, mister?
-We are just two
simple travelers.
-You two can pretend to
be human all you want,
but you can't fool my nose.
-And what are you
gonna do about it?
-(VOICEOVER) I
can't draw my sword.
But they're real demons!
Aw, who are you kidding?
-Oh, dear.
-All right, what the hell's
going on, you dish rag?
Those were real
demons, and you still
wouldn't let me draw Tetsusaiga.
-That's because
neither of these demons
was the one who stole my organs.
-Well, that's confusing.
-Indeed.
Not only have the villagers
been changed to look demons,
but there are unrelated
demons in the mix, too.
-Great.
More chains.
Just what I need.
-Those are for assaulting
innocent demons.
-This is an outrage!
You have disrupted the
tranquility of our village.
-Lay down your
weapons and surrender.
-Get on, Kagome.
-OK.
[groanign]
-Keep this up, and your
sword will disappear.
-Shut up.
-This way!
-So why did you help us, kid?
-Because I was scared.
My mother's not well.
She's been bedridden
since last night.
So I went out to get
her some medicine.
When I returned,
the whole village
was swarming with demons.
-I can't take it.
-She must have been transformed
by some demonic magic,
like all the other villagers.
WOMAN: Genosuke.
-Huh?
WOMAN: Is that you, my son?
-The demonic energy that
is emanating from your body
is most certainly that
of my internal organs.
-Ha.
So what if it is, old man?
Are you going to
cut open my belly
and try to take them back?
-So, this is your
true form, huh?
I can't use my sword.
What's going on?
-Do you need your sword,
or do you want it?
-What?
-Just stand back, Inuyasha.
-We can take care of this one.
-Whoa!
-Miroku!
Sango!
(VOICEOVER) What just happened?
Did the demon do that?
-Looks lke your friends
have flown away.
-I think now would
be a good time
to get rid of those chains.
-Ha.
You read my mind.
-Ah!
Huh?
It burned me.
Tetsusaiga doesn't
want me to draw.
[laughter]
-What are you waiting for?
Or is that sword on your
hip just decoration?
-Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
-You cannot just
slash at the thing.
Find the demon vortex.
-Demon vortex?
-Silence, you old wind bag!
-Why me?
-Iron Reaver Soul Stealer!
It's useless.
What was that demon
vortex nonsense
the old dish rag
was talking about?
Demonic energy?
[laughter]
-My demonic venom shall
dissolve your flesh.
-Inuyasha!
Hang in there.
Huh?
-Huh?
-Oh, no!
Genosuke?
-You must not interfere.
-Wah!
-Kagome!
I'm coming!
(VOICEOVER) Damn.
It's filling up
with demonic venom.
Huh?
Spirals of demonic energy?
The demon vortex!
-Ha ha ha!
Nice try, but you don't even
know what you're looking for.
-(VOICEOVER) One of
these is the real one.
Where?
Where is it?
Where's the real vortex?
I smell it.
Blades of Blood!
One of them smells
different than the others.
[scream]
-Inuyasha!
-Kagome, are you OK?
Huh?
Insense.
This must have
been what I smelled
coming from the demon vortex.
The demonic energy
hasn't changed,
which means the real demon
must be hiding somewhere else.
-You're right.
Nothing's changed.
The villagers are
still under that spell.
-And the seal on Tetsusaiga
hasn't been broken yet.
It's that smell again.
-Huh?
-Dish rag.
-What's happened to you?
-While the snake woman kept
you busy, I dispoed of him.
-So, you two were
working together.
-Now his organs are part
of my own flesh and blood.
-How dare you do that
to the old dish rag.
-You are the one at
fault, half demon.
We know your sword has the
power to absorb demonic energy.
Naturally, we cannot afford
to ignore such a weapon,
nor can we allow your technique
with it to be perfected.
That's why you attacked
a defenseless old man
and stole his organs?
-A necessary sacrifice.
-You're going to pay for that!
-You can't draw your sword
until the seal of the Great Holy
Demon Spirit placed
on it has been lifted.
-That won't matter if you're
the one we've been looking for.
If the dish rag was killed
for trying to help me,
the least I can do
is avenge his death.
The seal will break!
Huh?
Tetsusaiga-- Dragon
Scale Tetsusaiga!
-You can see my demon
vorteces, but you
can't tell which one
is real, can you?
INUYASHA: It's that one.
I'm sure of it.
Prepare yourself!
I can't move my sword.
I'm not going as easily
as the snake woman.
-The demonic energy--
-It seems you're giong to
need a better strategy.
-One way or another,
I'm gonna cut you down!
[coughing]
-This smell--
-Every attack on
me only increases
the damange to you and
your sword, you fool.
-Tetsusaiga's cracking.
-The demonic energy that I have
consumed from the Great Holy
Demon Spirit is inexhaustible!
-(VOICEOVER) The real demon
vortex is somewhere else.
-Take this!
-(VOICEOVER) The demonic
energy I was exposed
to, and the demonic
energy coming from the ox
demon's body.
They smell the same, but I
smell something stronger, too.
It's behind him!
Kagome, let go of
the dish rag, now!
-Huh?
-Turning your back on me?
-I can't see it, but
I know it's there.
I see it.
One strike will end this.
Hang in there, Tetsusaiga!
KAGOME: Everything's
back to normal.
-Kagome.
-Looks like we all made it.
-The spell that was on the
village has been broken, too.
-You did well to find
the real demon vortex.
-Dish rag?
You're still alive?
-Yes.
And the time has finally
come to you my true form.
Well, here it is.
I am sorry to have deceived you.
-I hate to break it to
you, but you don't really
look any different.
-Well, this one's less flat.
-Given your sudden
transformation,
I'm assuming you
weren't entirely
honest about your
organs being still.
-Correct.
-But what about the snake
woman and the ox demon?
-All a part of my illusion.
-You bastard.
What was the point of
this whole charade, then?
-What was the point?
To retrain you, of course.
-To retrain me?
-Isn't that why you came
to me in the first place?
I had to teach you how to
find true demonic energy.
But there was the other
thing you needed to learn.
-What is the other thing?
-Yes, what is it?
-Well, knowledge is
a river whose waters
must be drunk slowly.
-Tell me now.
-As you wish.
Basically, in the
illusionary world
that I created as a
backdrop for your training,
you were constantly exposed
to my demonic energy.
As a result, your
eyes were quickly
trained to spot demon vortices.
-Why all the chains
on his sword?
-I arranged for it to snap if
it were drawn unnecessarily.
-(VOICEOVER) So that's why
Tetsusaiga wouldn't allow me
to draw.
-But the real
purpose of all this
was to teach you how to use
the Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga.
-How to use it?
-I have a message
for you from Totosai.
Tetsusaiga is not meant
to absorb demonic energy.
Rather, the sword is
meant to cut through it.
-(VOICEOVER) It
cuts demonic energy?
-Tell me this.
Why did you decide to cut
that last demon vortex?
-Well, I noticed
Tetsusaiga was cracked.
So I needed to end the
fight in one strike.
-Oh, I can see the
theory was lost on you.
Still, what is truly important
is that you and your sword
are connected.
That is all.
Go on.
Draw Tetsusaiga.
-That's demonic energy.
-Did that all come from the
Great Holy Demon Spirit?
-It is because you cut
through my demon vortex.
My demonic energy
is strong enough
to slice your average
demon vortex in two.
-Great Holy Demon Spirit,
I'm sorry for judging you
by your appearance.
-Don't you mean, thank
you very much, Inuyasha?
-(VOICEOVER) I took him to be
an unreliable half demon brat.
But he did complete my training.
However, Tetsusaiga still
has one last form left,
and Inuyasha, I'm
afraid you'll have
to discover that
one on your own.
[theme music]
NARAKU: I had this specially
prepared just for you.
You'd be wise to accept
it and return to my body.
KAGOME: Naraku has absorbed
the demon tree Yomeiju.
It's all a part of a
secret plan to get closer
to the infant, his heart.
Now, with Koga and his
Shikon jewel shards,
along with Inuyasha
and company, it
looks like the battle
between the three groups
will finally come to an end.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"Inuyasha, The Final
Act," the End of Moryomaru.
-Damn you, Naraku.
-So you intend to
take me down with you.