[music playing]
[theme music]
-Ah!
InuYasha!
-Yes, Tessaiga!.
Ah.
-(THINKING) I'll
have only one chance.
Get away!
-[gasp] I can't move.
-He's trying to move to Kagome.
-It hurts.
InuYasha.
Dragon scale Tessaiga?
What?
-I'm being forced out.
-What's wrong?
Have you given up hiding
in other people's bodies?
-[roaring]
-You couldn't have
picked a worse person
to try and possess.
-No.
I can not lose to the demonic
energy of a half demon!
-Tessaiga!
It's over, Magatsuhi.
-Impossible!
INUYASHA: Naraku,
the trap of light.
-[screaming]
-(THINKING) This sensation,
it's like a fog has lifted.
-Kagome.
-My spiritual power
is returning to me.
Huh?
-Huh?
-Whoa.
INUYASHA: Kagome!
Huh?
-InuYasha?
InuYasha, look at you.
-Kagome.
-You're back to normal.
I'm so glad.
-Yeah, I am.
Thanks to your powers
of purification.
-It's all because Sesshomaru
cut down Magatsuhi.
Thank you.
Sesshomaru?
-(THINKING) I smell her.
That's Rin's scent.
Everything's much clearer now.
Did Kagome's
spiritual power purge
Naraku's body of demonic energy?
-Huh?
-What's going on?
-You think Naraku's
noticed we're here yet?
-Wah!
-Master Jaken!
-Whoa!
-Shippo!
-I'll be fine.
No need to panic.
Help me, Kohaku!
Jaken!
-Kohaku!
Shippo!
I don't want to die alone.
Help!
-Why is he attacking
us all of a sudden?
-InuYasha, we have to
find the Shikon Jewel.
-Yeah.
We should hurry.
All this shaking must mean
that Naraku is finally
getting serious
about eliminating us.
-(THINKING) Although
it is faint,
a light has returned
to the Shikon Jewel.
That can only mean that
Magatsuhi has been destroyed.
And that Kagome's purification
powers have returned.
For InuYasha and his group,
the return of this light
would likely be viewed
as a sign of hope.
[chuckling] However,
I shall soon
mold it into a ray of despair.
-Light?
-Huh?
NARAKU: So you've noticed.
-Naraku.
NARAKU: Rejoice.
Light has returned
to the Shikon Jewel.
Though I suspect you're
not the only ones
who are going to notice.
-Shut up.
I'm tired of listening
to your damn nonsense.
NARAKU: I'm sure your friends
will also see this light.
-You mean Miroku and Sango?
NARAKU: [chuckling] Yes.
What do you suppose
they're doing right now?
Also, what will they think
upon seeing this light?
-Huh?
What are you getting at?
NARAKU: I shall give
you a small hint.
Miroku's wind tunnel is
dangerously close to its limit.
I'm sure you know
what will happen
the next time he uses it.
-Huh?
-The shaking has stopped.
What now?
I could open my wind
tunnel right here,
do minor damage to
Naraku before perishing.
Pathetic.
Here I am inside Naraku,
yet I'm unable to do
so much as wound him.
-Miroku, where are you?
Miroku?
-Sango, we must part ways.
-[gasp]
-Farewell.
-Wait.
Why?
Does he intend to die alone?
I can't go on without him.
I just can't.
-Now then, it looks like
it's beginning to sink in.
You see, Miroku has
parted ways with Sango,
and is now wandering alone.
He's obviously trying to avoid
drawing Sango into his wind
tunnel when it
finally destroys him.
-Huh? (THINKING) Light?
Pure light?
Is it-- it must be the
light from the Shikon Jewel.
Has Kagome's spiritual
power returned?
I can follow it all the way to
the Shikon Jewel, to Naraku.
I can destroy him if my
wind tunnel will just
hold until I get there.
NARAKU: [chuckling]
Assured of his purpose,
he hastens to his death.
Meanwhile, there is
another who fears
his death more than anything.
-(THINKING) Light?
That's, that's from
the Shikon Jewel.
I'm sure of it.
That light should lead
me right to Naraku.
If I destroy him, the
curse will be lifted.
No more wind tunnel.
There's still a chance I
can save Miroku's life.
I have to find that Jewel.
Kirara!
Just you wait, Naraku
-Your friends,
they will no doubt
follow the light to
find me, won't they?
But There's no guarantee
that's what they'll find.
-Coward.
You think you can trick Miroku
into opening his wind tunnel
one last time, don't you?
--[chuckling] Kagome, your
light will be the death
of your friends.
-Adamant barrage!
-Nothing.
-Ah, didn't even flinch.
Now what?
Do we get out of here, and keep
looking for the Shikon Jewel?
-First, let's find Miroku.
We can't let him
use his wind tunnel.
Right.
--[chucking] You'll
never make it in time.
-Found you.
-You've done well to reach
me so quickly, Sango.
In fact, you're the
first to arrive.
-[gasp] Rin!
-Now you can destroy me,
the Shikon Jewel, too.
-You let her go.
-I see.
You won't throw
Hiraikotsu if Rin is here.
You won't do it, even though
this is the perfect opportunity
to kill me.
You are far too gentle.
But your gentleness
will kill the monk.
-What do you mean by that?
-Come now, Sango.
You should know
very well without my
having to explain it.
The monk will follow a light
he believes to be the Jewel.
Next he'll encounter an
illusion he believes to be me.
In a futile attempt to
destroy his hated foe,
he will open his wind
tunnel one last time.
-The light is glowing brighter.
I'm almost there.
-You've done well to
reach me so quickly, monk.
In fact, you're the
first to arrive.
-[grunting]
-We're close.
I can smell Miroku.
-I can sense that
we're moving away
from the real Shikon Jewel.
So Naraku is trying
to trick Miroku
into opening his wind
tunnel, and killing himself.
--[chuckling] Tell me, what
does this girl mean to you?
Sango, you barely
know her, right?
So I ask you, is it really worth
sacrificing the monk's life
to protect this child?
-(THINKING) My, my.
Naraku's been busy.
It's a lot of work to create all
these illusions for everyone.
Although I see that the Rin
girl is no illusion at all.
-(THINKING) No, I don't
want Miroku to die,
even if I go to Hell for this,
I'm going to save his life.
-(THINKING) Very good, Sango.
Kill Rin, and save
your beloved monk.
-(THINKING) Rin.
-(THINKING) I don't care if
my wind tunnel tears open,
as long as I'm able to take
Naraku and the Shikon Jewel
with me.
-(THINKING) Miroku, no
matter what he shows you,
don't open your wind tunnel!
Miroku, you better not
open your wind tunnel.
-Miroku!
-Don't do it!
-Good.
Now open your wind tunnel.
-Miroku, no!
It's an illusion
-Adamant barrage!
--[chuckling] Why
do you hesitate?
Go on.
Or are you too afraid, monk?
-I don't think Miroku's
able to see us.
-Yeah.
He didn't react to
adamant barrage, either.
The only thing Miroku can see
is that illusion of Naraku.
And I bet Naraku is hoping
we'll be sucked into the wind
tunnel, along with his illusion.
-Miroku, the great savior.
Seems you'd rather save
yourself than your friends.
MIROKU: Forgive me, Sango.
I wanted to be with you forever.
That's enough, Naraku!
Wind tunnel--
-Miroku!
I won't let you.
Kagome, the beads.
-Right.
-That was a way too close.
If he had opened his wind tunnel
any sooner, we'd all be dead.
--[chuckling] In the end,
you chose to save yourself.
You've lost your attachments
to this world, monk.
-Silence.
I shall take you with me now.
-Hey, snap out of it.
Don't you recognize me?
-We have to get rid
of this illusion.
-[chuckling]
-It's still there?
Of course it is.
And it won't disappear,
not until the monk is dead,
and I've seen just how far Sango
will go in order to save him.
-What does that mean?
-What is this?
Rin!
Sister!
Oh no.
She's about to show
throw Hiraikotsu.
-(THINKING) If I Naraku, than
Miroku's life will be saved.
-Stop!
Don't do it, sister.
Please stop.
BYAKUYA: Hello, Kohaku.
-Huh?
What are you doing here?
-Just be quiet, and watch.
I assure you, your sister
can't hear your voice, anyway.
KOHAKU: What are
you talking about?
-The human heart is
easily manipulated,
especially in the case of your
sister, whose heart is consumed
with the fear of losing
her beloved monk.
-(THINKING) If I don't
defeat Naraku now,
the wind tunnel
will pass its limit.
And Miroku will end up
just like his father.
I can't bear to let that happen.
-(THINKING) Sango, your weakness
is the perfect complement
to the darkness of
the Shikon Jewel.
-(THINKING) The darkness of
the Shikon Jewel has purged
my purifying light.
--[chuckling] It appears
Sango has fallen.
KAGOME: (THINKING) The
light will be swallowed.
I have to stop this before
Naraku recovers his power.
But how?
What am I supposed to shoot?
-Kagome?
KAGOME: (THINKING)
Look carefully.
I see it, his real boy.
This better work!
-Forgive me, Rin!
-Sister!
--[chuckling] As soon as Sango's
Hiraikotsu destroys Rin,
the Shikon Jewel will once
again be filled with darkness.
-(THINKING) It disappeared.
-(THINKING) It's
just like before,
when I shot Lady Hitomiko.
It'll work.
I just have to wait.
My arrow will hit Naraku.
-Hmm?
-[gasp]
-Rin!
-Kohaku?
-It's OK.
Rin's going to be all right.
-You tried to kill
her, didn't you?
Along with the illusion of
Naraku that I showed you.
-(THINKING) Illusion?
BYAKUYA: You were
going to sacrifice
Rin, if it meant saving the
monk's life, weren't you?
-(THINKING) I--
-I'm afraid it doesn't really
matter how you spin it.
The fact is, you were
weighing human lives
against one another.
It's fitting, really.
The demon slayer
Sango slays herself.
Whoopsie.
-Lord Sesshomaru!
-(THINKING) Sesshomaru.
-If that was intended
for me, you've
got the wrong
person, Sesshomaru.
But my guess is you were
listening to our conversation.
So I'll leave you
two to settle this.
Bye now.
(THINKING) Boy, I sure don't
like the looks of this.
It seems his real body
has taken a serious blow.
But I suppose if
I'm still here, it
must be proof that Naraku
and the Shikon Jewel
are still in one piece.
I guess the time has
come to use this.
-Sesshomaru, if you
wish to kill me,
I will not try to resist you.
-Sister, what are you saying?
Lord Sesshomaru, please.
Rin is safe.
Forgive my sister.
-There's no excuse.
I tried to kill Rin.
-My sister was deceived
by an illusion of Naraku.
-It doesn't change the fact that
I was ready to sacrifice her.
I would've done anything
to defeat Naraku, anything!
-Sister.
-I will not attempt to justify
it, or beg for my life.
But please, let me finish this.
Once the curse has been lifted
from Miroku, I'm all yours.
-Sister.
-InuYasha, please
leave me behind.
-I can't do that.
If I leave you alone,
there's a good chance
another illusion of
Naraku might trick you
into opening your wind tunnel.
-It could tear
open at any moment.
If it does, you'll
be sucked in with me.
-Hah, it's going to take more
than your dumb wind tunnel
to scare me away.
-Besides, if we ever
make it out of here,
Sango's going to need
you in one piece.
-Yeah.
We need you, Miroku.
We're all going home alive.
-The light!
-(THINKING) The
smell has changed.
Naraku is in the
direction of the light.
Hurry.
-Huh?
-You want to find
the monk, don't you?
-Hey, sister, let's go.
-Yes, right.
(THINKING) Does
this mean Sesshomaru
is going to wait to kill me
until after Naraku is defeated?
Is Miroku even still alive?
I have to see him one last time.
INUYASHA: Naraku!
-The light is
returning to the Jewel.
-I see it, too.
That means your arrow
must have hit him.
-You found me, InuYasha.
You do realize this is your
only chance to kill me.
-I don't need you to tell me to
send you and the Shikon Jewel
to the under world.
Meido Zangetsuha!
-[gasp]
--[chuckling] Looks
like you missed.
-Impossible.
-[panting] A light.
Where is it coming from?
Huh? [screaming]
It's InuYasha's
Meido Zangetsuha.
That's as close as I
ever want to get to it.
Huh?
[panting] That's
Byakuya of the Dreams.
-I guess the time has
finally come to draw this.
-Huh? (THINKING)
There's no blade.
What?
How did he just do that?
-Yoohoo.
You can come out now.
-Hey, what did you just do, huh?
-You saw that?
-I took some of Meido
Zangetsuha's demonic energy.
Naraku told me to collect some.
-Collect some?
How dare you do that?
Meido Zangetsuha is a technique
that Sesshomaru and InuYasha
had to work for.
You can't just show
up and take it.
-(THINKING) It's true.
That's why this sword
can only be used once.
I have no idea how
Naraku intends to use it.
But I do know that
the end is near.
Oh, this is your last chance to
escape before the hole closes.
-Huh?
So you're not going
to capture me?
Why not?
--[chuckling] Don't
forget, InuYasha,
light and dark may be battling
against each other in here.
But until you defeat me,
I control this place.
-That's enough of your lies.
[gasp]
-His miasma.
-Damn it!
-InuYasha.
-Huh?
-Hey, Rin, you're awake.
-Kohaku.
You'll be safe now.
-Lord Sesshomaru!
-It's miasma.
Sister.
-Rin, I'm sorry.
-Huh?
-I'm going ahead.
-You can't go without
your protective mask.
-(THINKING) So she's
risking her life.
-Have you noticed
anything different?
This miasma is much more potent.
In fact, it is
deadly, especially
for weak humans like
Kagome and the monk.
-(THINKING) He's not
taking any chances.
Yo must be getting
desperate, Naraku.
-(THINKING) Naraku is
afraid of my arrow.
He doesn't want me to shoot.
-This won't be enough
to get rid of us.
Prepare yourself, Naraku!
I'm coming for you!
[music playing]
-It would seem the
time has finally
come for me to fulfill my role.
-Give up, Naraku.
It's all over.
KAGOME: InuYasha's
Meido Zangetsuha
and Sesshomaru's Bakusaiga
are overwhelming Naraku.
But why, Naraku?
NARAKU: The Shikon
Jewel will never
disappear from this world.
Even if I am destroyed,
it will live on.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"InuYasha, The Final Act"--
Naraku's Uncertain Wish.
KAGOME: Naraku, what were you
even trying to accomplish?