[theme music]
[children playing]
(SINGING) Ka- go-
me, Ka- go- me,
you are no more than
a bird in a cage.
(CHILDREN SINGING) Crane and
a turtle gonna slip and fall.
Who's behind you now?
Are they big or small?
-It's Mitsko!
[gasp]
-My name is Naraku, I have come
for your life, Lady Hitomiko.
Do not be afraid.
My, my, very impressive, indeed.
Your barrier withstood
my miasma with ease.
If this is any
indication, it would
be both dangerous
and unwise for me
to ignore your spiritual power.
-Hitomiko, run home!
-Master, help me!
-What you see here is a demon!
I summon the divine
to drive you from us!
-(CHUCKLING) Is that the
extent of your spiritual power?
-Augh!
[gasping]
-Master, no!
Are you OK?
[evil laughter]
-You hurt him!
Now demon-- be gone!
-Ugh!
Ahh!
-Mm, it escaped, huh?
-Master, be strong!
-Hitomiko, though you are
young, your spiritual powers
rival that of Lady Kikyo, who
passed away many years ago.
Your gift makes you a threat
to evil spirits and demons,
and they will seek
to destroy you.
Promise me that you will
not neglect your training.
-Master, please.
-Though you did not choose
this fight, it is yours.
[mournful cry]
-That was 15 years ago.
He was right.
Since then I have spent
my life fighting demons.
I did not choose this life, but
such is my fate as a priestess.
-Lady Hitomiko!
Lady Hitomiko!
It's terrible.
We found a traveler who's
collapsed by the entrance
to the village!
-If we try to carry
him into the village,
there's a good chance the
disease may end up spreading.
-Perhaps we should just
put him out of his misery.
-Let me see him.
Tell me, traveler.
What is it that ails you?
[loud roar]
-Aahh!
-Lady Hitomiko, what happened?
-Do not worry.
The village is safe.
I have slain the demon.
[gasp]
[evil laughter]
-I know that voice.
-Is she breathing?
-Hitomiko's Barrier
-I'm positive.
Those are Naraku's spider webs.
-Really?
I can't see a thing!
-Only Kagome is able
to see them, Shippo.
-Damn you, Naraku!
Those webs are what he used
to defile and kill Kikyo!
What's he plotting this time?
-This is where they
originate from?
-Yes, up there by the shrine.
-Uh, who are you people?
-Are you from the village?
I don't mean to pry, but
I feel I must ask you.
Has anything unusual happened
here in the past few days.
Something happened
here didn't it?
-Actually, something did
happen to Lady Hitomiko--
the priestess who used
to protect our village.
-I was too careless.
It seems a thread
from that demon's web
has fastened to my back.
-Lady Hitomiko!
-I don't have long to live now.
-That can't be!
-You mustn't lose hope.
It has been so
long, and I'm tired.
Besides, I was supposed
to have died 15 years ago.
If I die, I want you to
promise me you'll sever my head
and bury it separately
from my body.
VILLAGER: And with those
final instructions,
Lady Hitomiko passed away.
However, none of us
could bring ourselves
to do what she'd asked.
So we buried her whole.
And then something happened.
[gasps]
-What is this?
Do we have visitors?
[recoiling in fear]
-Lady Hitomiko!
-I take it this is the
priestess who died.
-She came back to life?
-No, she's dead--
no doubt about it.
There's no mistaking
the smell of a corpse.
-Spider webs!
-Hey!
Even I can see them this time.
-So I gather you must be Kagome.
-Huh?
Wait, how do you know my name?
-Listen, Kagome, you must
leave this place immediately.
Turn away and never look back.
Otherwise, I'll be
forced to kill you.
-Ha!
Is that supposed to scare us?
Yaaa!
-You are a fool!
You will never destroy me
by severing the spider webs!
-Was that her?
-It must be a demon that's
taken the form of Lady Hitomiko.
-Not quite.
A demon named Naraku
has taken control
of Lady Hitomiko's body.
-Isn't there anything
we can do to save her?
-At this point, all we can
do is recover her remains.
-Whatever the case, we must
do what we can to help her.
She would not have wanted this.
I presume she made
that dying wish
to avoid this very situation.
-I beg of you, if we could
at least honor her remains,
it would mean everything.
-I understand.
We'll do what we
can to help you.
-NARAKU: Hitomiko, how
things have changed.
Now that I hold the
Shikon Jewel, not even
you can overcome my power.
-Damn you, Naraku.
-Don't be unkind.
After all, you were
tired from battling
demons all those years.
You wished it would end, and
now I've granted your wish.
And now, as a token
of your gratitude,
there's something I
need you to do for me.
Yes, Hitomiko, there's one
final task you must perform.
You will steal Kagome's power,
and then you'll destroy her.
It should be easy for you.
-Oh no!
Lady Hitomiko's shrine is
covered with spider webs!
-Well, It looks like
an invitation to me.
-Aahh!
-The webs!
-Everyone stand back!
-Tessaiga is not working!
-[inaudible] did it!
-A barrier!
-Your weapons are
powerless against me.
A priestess's barrier can
only be broken by a priestess.
-What are those?
[bells ringing]
-Bells?
It looks like they're
holding the barrier together.
All I have to do is shoot one,
and the barrier will collapse.
-You got it!
-Hm, we are connected.
-Huh?
-Kagome!
-I'm being sucked in!
-She vanished!
-Damn it!
Inuyasha, we can't do
anything about this barrier.
Naraku, that bastard!
He was after Kagome
from the very beginning?
-Lady Hitomiko!
-I don't understand.
What point is there in
stealing your feeble power?
I wonder what Naraku was
hoping to accomplish.
-Lady Hitomiko, I
came to your shrine
because I want to save you!
-Oh really?
You propose to save me, do you?
How absurd!
-Kagome, do you think it
was by chance that you
were given the name Kagome?
-Huh?
-That name you bear
holds a special power--
a power hidden within you
since the day you were born.
-I don't understand.
Why is she telling me this?
-Humph!
You are no more than
a bird in a cage.
You shall never leave-- never.
-I can't move!
Naraku!
Stop hiding up there
and show yourself!
You're a coward!
-She can still move?
Now I see it is not
you he is after.
I am supposed to steal the power
that resides within that bow.
-This bow?
The bow I received
on Mount Azusa.
-If I'm not mistaken,
that bow was originally
meant to be wielded by another.
A person who would have been
able to master the use of it.
[gasp]
-Kikyo!
-You merely aim and
release with it,
unable to harness
its spiritual power.
And yet, you believe
you can save me?
Leave the bow here,
and be on your way.
Do so, and your
life will be spared.
But take it with you,
and you shall die.
-NARAKU: You'll spare
her life, will you?
Then you leave me no choice!
-Show yourself, Naraku!
-Do not waste your arrows.
-NARAKU: Indeed.
If you must shoot, aim here.
-There's a spider in her chest!
-NARAKU: Shoot the
arrow through her chest.
Once you do, Hitomiko
will finally die,
and you will be saved.
-I won't do it!
I won't take orders
from you, Naraku!
-Then you leave me no
choice, but to kill you.
[gasps]
-NARAKU: Now then,
will you shoot
her to save your own life?
-It broke the spell!
-It's use!
[evil laughter]
-You cannot escape
Hitomiko's barrier!
-Naraku!
-NARAKU: The only way to
escape is to destroy Hitomiko!
Will you refuse to fight,
and allow her to kill you?
Or will you shoot the
spider nesting within her,
and win your freedom?
You can only choose one.
But before you do, I
should tell you this.
If you destroy Hitomiko
with your sacred arrow,
her soul can never be saved.
[gasp]
-NARAKU: The priestess will die
a demon, and so will her soul.
Which means it will be
cursed to join my spider
webs in the fires of
hell for all eternity.
You'd do well to
keep that in mind.
One more thing.
Now that I've told
you this, should you
choose to shoot
Hitomiko, your heart
will be corrupted for
all eternity, as well.
-Shut up!
I've heard enough of
your talk, Naraku!
-NARAKU: Either
outcome suits me fine.
You surrender and allow
Himotiko to kill you,
or you sacrifice Hitomiko to
save your own life, thereby
corrupting your heart.
A heart so vile that it is
capable of condemning Hitomiko
to hell for personal
gain, will surely
fall victim to my spider webs.
Corrupt Kagome, and steal her
spiritual power, Hitomiko.
And you, Kagome, know that
within Hitomiko's barrier,
you must kill or be killed.
-Those flames are made
with your blood, Kagome.
I'm afraid they'll only
intensify as you get closer.
If I use my bow
and fight, I won't
be able to save Lady Hitomiku!
What should I do?
-Yaaa!
Ugh!
Damn it!
-Even the barrier-breaking
tessaiga can't break it?
-Kagome!
-I'm sure Lady Hitomiko was
trying to tell me something.
-You merely aim and
release with it--
unable to harness
its spiritual power.
-So if I learn how to
use the bow properly,
I can save Lady Hitomiko?
I already know that Naraku
wants me to shoot her.
But I would never
be able to do that.
Besides, even if it got me out
of this situation, then what?
My heart would be so
corrupt that I'd never
be able to escape
Naraku's spider webs.
What is this?
An illusion?
-This is no illusion.
You are in hell!
You will answer me!
Why were you given
the name Kagome?
If you cannot understand
that, you are destined to be
incinerated by
the fires of hell!
You must remember!
-Stop!
This is the hand of the demon!
-Can you feel the pain?
Are you burning up?
Though it may feel that way,
this fire will never kill you.
But you will suffer this
pain for all eternity.
-It's so hot!
Please help me!
-Cry all you want.
But no one can save
you now, foolish girl!
You dare to talk of
saving me, but you
have no power to speak of.
You can't even save yourself!
-Maybe shooting that
spider is my only choice.
But when she was choking me
just now, with this hand,
I sensed a strong
emotion from her.
But what was it?
Was it fear?
No.
No, worse!
It was a deep sorrow.
I can't allow myself to
leave this person here.
-Why were you given
the name Kagome?
-Why was I given
-There, there.
That's a good girl.
You're my precious
little Kagome.
Ka- go- me.
Hello there, Kagome.
-There, there.
That's right.
Mama, um, how come
I was named Kagome?
-Huh?
Why do you ask, sweetheart?
Well, you see, everyone
makes fun of me.
They sing, Ka- go-
me, Ka- go- me.
-(SIGHING) I see.
I'm sorry, but
that's what I saw.
-What did you see?
-Well, it might sound silly,
but when you were born,
I saw something like this
shining on your chest.
And the star-like shape
is known as a kagome.
-Oh.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
The Shikon Jewel had been hidden
within my body from birth.
When I was born, my mom must've
been able to see its light.
Which means, my name,
Kagome, actually
came from the Shikon Jewel.
But so what?
It still doesn't mean I was
born with any special powers.
I don't understand!
I don't know what
you're talking about!
-In that case, down
into hell you go!
-(CHILD'S TAUNTING
VOICE) Kagome!
Let's play Kago- me, Kagome!
-I always hated
that game so much!
The other kids would
make a circle--
-(CHILDREN SINGING)
Ka- gome, Ka- go- me,
you are no more than a bird--
-LADY HITOMIKO: You
merely aim and release
with it-- unable to harness
it's spiritual power.
--who's behind you now?
Are they big or small?
LADY HITOMIKO:
You must remember!
Why?
Why are you Kagome?
-Who's behind you now?
Are they big or small?
-It's Heedae!
-Huh?
But how did you know it was me?
-I don't know how.
I just knew.
I can't help it, all right?
I couldn't explain
it, but I knew.
Every time we played, I knew
exactly who was behind me.
[gasp]
-Is that it?
Could that be the
power I was born with?
Who's behind me?
Naraku!
I want to save Lady Hitomiko.
If I can somehow combine the
spiritual power of this bow
with my power, I can do it!
The shape of that
light-- I see it!
This is what Lady
Hitomiko was trying
to tell me when she
asked about my name!
Please bow of Mount
Azusa I'm begging
you to lend me your strength.
Pierce the light of that
star, and set her free!
Take this!
[evil laughter]
-The arrow disappeared?
[gasp]
-Augh!
[groan]
-I did it!
Amazing!
So this is the true
spiritual power of the bow!
[gasps]
-What's this?
-The spider webs
are disappearing,
-And the barrier has vanished.
-It must've been Kagome!
-Let's go!
[moaning]
-Huh?
-It is all over.
You are a true mystery.
[gasp]
-In the end, you
were able to combine
your own power and the
spiritual power of the bow
to shatter the evil
presence that bound me.
You saved me, Kagome--
that much I understand.
However, it was
only in the moment
you released the arrow that
your power became visible.
Something is sealing
your true power--
what it is, I do not know.
-Huh?
-Lady Hitomiko!
-Kagome, you are such a
mysterious person-- the source
of your power, and
even your name.
-Kagome!
-Kagome, are you OK?
-Inuyasha!
-She is already passed on.
-But it seems that
she's finally at peace.
[chattering]
-VILLAGER: At last, Lady
Hitomiko can rest in peace.
-Please erect a memorial to
honor her life in service
to this village.
[sound of birds]
-What's the matter, Kagome?
You haven't said a
word since we left.
-It's nothing.
I'm fine.
LADY HITOMIKO: It was
only in the moment
you released the arrow, that
your power became visible.
-If what Lady Hitomiko
said was true,
my power is being sealed
by something-- or someone.
Kikyo, maybe?
Or perhaps--
[theme music]
-You are weak!
The evil will of the demon
sealed within the Shikon Jewel
called Magatsuhi borrows the
bodies of Naraku's demons
to appear in this
world, and attacks
the Shubaru, and his companions.
You must escape, Master Shubaru!
If you were to lose
your right arm,
you would no longer
be able to fight!
Next time on Iriasha--
The Final Act.
Magatsuhi's Evil Will.
MAGATSUHI: You must
die by my hand!
My very pride is at stake.