[theme music]
[roar]
-Masterful.
Masterful, Lord Sesshomaru.
-A technique that cuts
through to the underworld.
TOTOSAI: Instead of just
wounding your opponent
in battle, the
master of Tenseiga
cuts a path to the
underworld, and in doing
so sends your enemy there.
That is how you use t.
And the name for that
technique is Meido Zangetsuha.
At present, you can only achieve
a Crescent Moonlight Cut,
but once your
technique is perfected,
you will be able to cut
a complete circle that
will instantly swallow your foe,
sending him to the next world.
-It seems i have much to learn.
TOTOSAI: The demon
blade Dakki, huh?
-Come on, you must know
something about it.
-Well, yes, I have heard of it.
Take a look at this.
-What is that thing?
-One of Ryujin's scales.
-I've heard of this sword.
The legendary Dakki.
-This one is a failed attempt,
hardly worthy of the name.
-A failed attempt?
That thing absorbed all of
Tetsusaiga's demonic energy.
Naturally, it still wasn't
enough to defeat me.
-If the blade bad been
successfully forged,
you wouldn't be here.
-Are you saying it's
possible there's
a real one like this somewhere?
-Why would you ask such a thing?
-Well, if Tetsusaiga
had the ability
to absorb demonic
energy like that,
then fighting Naraku and
Moryomaru would be easier.
-Out of the question.
To achieve that
kind of power, you'd
have to fight against Dakki.
If you were to
lose such a battle,
and all of Tetsusaiga's demonic
energy were to be absorbed,
it'd be just a rusty
blade, incapable of being
returned to its original form.
Tell me, Inuyasha, is that a
risk you're willing to take?
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga.
[grunting]
-I've done it.
I've finally managed to combine
Ryujin's scales with a blade.
[shouting]
-It's a monster!
-Toshu!
Show yourself!
Where are you hiding?
Right here?
So you've finally
completed Dakki.
Hand it over to me.
Now.
-Wind Scar!
[scream]
-Did you get him?
-Huh.
Didn't take much.
-Master, that man is most
definitely the swordsmith
Toshu.
I've heard that he's been
using Ryujin's scales
to attempt to forge Dakki.
-This must be where that
giant raccoon got his.
-He must have stolen
it from this guy.
-Is it possible for
a human to craft
a demon blade such as that?
-You must run!
Ryujin is alive, I assure you!
[roar]
-Now, I'm looking
forward to this.
-I suggest you
stand back, Toshu.
-You should let us handle this.
-Young fools, you
dare to protect Toshu?
Then I shall tear each
one of you limb from limb!
-Sounds like fun to me!
Damn.
Wind Scar!
[laughter]
-Is that all?
-Wind Scar!
-Attack me as many
times as you like.
My shield is invincible.
The more demonic
energy it's exposed to,
the stronger it gets.
[laughter]
-So this is the extent of
the wolf demon tribe's power?
How pathetic.
-Run for it, Shinta!
-Brother!
-What's this?
Leftovers?
-Yah!
-Kai!
-That won't do.
What would be the
point of this if you
don't leave any survivors?
There, there.
Don't be afraid, boy.
I'm going to lend you this.
It'll ease your pain,
and make you run faster.
-How about this?
Wind Scar!
-You're wasting your time.
-I'll smash that shield
of yours eventually.
-You amuse me.
You really think
your feeble attacks
will crack this
dragon scale shield?
Thanks to all your
attacks, I can give you
a taste of your own medicine.
-He absorbed all that energy.
-He's about to attack.
-Inuyasha, run away!
-Run away?
I don't think so.
-Now, die!
-This is what I've
been waiting for!
Backlash Wave!
-Ah!
-Oh, wow he did it!
-Brilliant!
The master must have known
that his best chance at victory
was to wait for an attack, then
hit him with the Backlash Wave.
-Brilliant?
This is Inuyasha we're
talking about, right?
-You bastard.
[groan]
-Why'd you do that?
-It's mine.
Ryujin's power is mine!
Now Dakki is finally complete.
-Huh?
MAN: Wait for us, Koga!
MAN: Let's rest for a bit.
KOGA: You're kidding, right?
We just took a break.
MAN: Just took a break?
That was a half day ago!
MAN: Are you trying to kill us?
-Man.
(VOICEOVER) What is that?
Something's closing in on us.
And fast.
Hit the ground!
-You're Koga, aren't you?
-That depends.
Who are you?
-My friends were all killed
because of you, all right?
I've come to take the Shikon
jewel shars in your legs!
-Don't be stupid.
You can't seriously believe
that you can defeat me,
you little brat.
-Oh, no?
-Wah!
-What's really
going on here, kid?
You have the stench of Naraku.
Is he behind this?
Is that why you're here?
Do you work for him?
-Course not!
-Then what are you doing here?
And why are you after
my Shikon jewel shards?
-(VOICEOVER) The sun's setting!
-Make sure you
return before sunset,
or you will never see
your brother again.
-Shinta!
-Get back here, brat!
I'm trying to tell you I want
to hear what you have to say!
-Uh, it didn't really
come across like that!
-Not even close!
-This sword is precious to me.
I would never hand it over
to you or anyone else.
On the other hand, I'm
very interested in that
blade you have there.
Dakki desires the demonic
energy in that sword.
-I say kill him and just
get it over with, Inuyasha.
Isn't that what we all want?
-Come on, Myoga.
-We came here with the intent to
get the Dakki's power, anyway.
So this should be a simple
task against a mere human.
-Simple minded as usual.
-A sword like that
won't do you any good.
You should know it's far too
powerful for an ordinary human
to handle.
-If that's true, then this
should be easy for you!
-Idiot!
-I can't believe he's able to
overpower Inuyasha like that.
-I wonder if Toshu
really is human?
-Of course I'm human, you fools!
It is because I am human that
I long for a powerful weapon.
So I devoted every
waking moment of my life
to forging the ultimate sword.
After forging
hundreds of swords,
I learned an important lesson.
The greater the infusion of
energy, the stronger the blade.
I scoured countless battlefields
in search of broken swords
that had absorbed the feelings
of regret and bitter blood.
On one such battlefield,
he found me.
-Human!
Your energy has summoned
I, Ryujin, to this place.
TOSHU: I trembled at the
sight, but it was with joy
more than fear.
Great Ryujin!
I beg of you, please allow
me to forge a sword for you.
-Very well.
Your wicked nature makes you
well suited to craft Dakki.
-And that is how Dakki was born.
Every time our blades cross,
Dakki's demonic presences
eats away at Tetsusaiga,
absorbing its demonic energy
little by little.
-There's a crack in Tetsusaiga!
-(VOICEOVER) Looks I'm gonna
have to shatter Dakki before it
absorbs all of
Tetsusaiga's energy.
Huh?
SHIPPO: The dragon scales are
spreading to Toshu's hands!
MIROKU: Dakki's demonic presence
is eating away at him as well.
-I'm trying to help you, Toshu.
You're running out of time.
Now drop that sword
before it's too late.
-Not until I've taken the last
of Tetsusaiga's demonic energy!
[laughter] I feel it
surging through me.
-Don't you understand?
If this keeps up, your whole
body will be consumed by Dakki.
-You're wrong!
Dakki has chosen me, and I alone
shall be the one to wield it!
-(VOICEOVER) I can't
lose this battle!
TOTOSAI (VOICEOVER) Tetsusaiga
would be just a rusty blade,
incapable of being returned
to its original form.
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
Hang in there, Tetsusaiga.
-What a strong gust
of demonic wind.
Dakki, you desire
that power, don't you?
-(VOICEOVER) Just hold together.
It won't be much longer.
-It will be ours, Dakki!
-One more time, Tetsusaiga!
KAGOME: Is that wind
protecting Inuyasha?
MYOGA: No!
Tetsusaiga's merely
avoiding contact with Dakki
by any means necessary.
The sword has reached its limit.
-What?
-(VOICEOVER) One more strike
is all it would take to destroy
Tetsusaiga.
It can't take much more of this.
-A barrier of wind, huh?
I know of one way to defeat
you without getting too close.
But you should know
that better than anyone.
-Wind Scar!
-Come on, Tetsusaiga!
Backlash Wave!
BYAKUA: As you can
see, the sun has set.
So, I assume you brought me
Koga's Shikon jewel shars?
-Where's Shinta?
Where's my brother?
-Ah-ha.
So you brought Koga
here in person, did you?
Well, I suppose that will work.
-That damn smell.
You're one of Naraku's
incarnations, huh?
-Let Shinta go!
-Stand back!
-I think I understand
what's going on here.
First you had that thing kill
this kid's fellow wolf demons.
Then, like cowards, you
took his brother hostage
so you could get
him to attack me.
Is that about right?
DEMON: So what if it is?
-I shall avenge the grievances
of the wolf demon tribe!
[laughter]
-These claws have been washed
in gallons of wolf demon blood.
And now they thirst
for your blood, too.
-Shut your mouth-- and die!
[scream]
-Oh.
-So much for him.
You're next, coward.
-Am I?
-After all, you were the one
commanding that beast to kill,
even if it was on
Naraku's orders.
-Yes, that's true.
But if you kill
me, I'm afraid you
might be putting his
brother's life at risk.
-Please help me.
-Where is he?
Tell me, or I swear
I'll kill you.
[muffled scream]
KAI: Shinta!
-Hey, wait up!
-You'd better hurry if
you wish to save him.
The demonic energy being
emitted by that moth
might make it quite appetizing
to larger predators.
-I've already come this far.
-Ha ha ha!
I've absorbed all the demonic
energy from the Backlash Wave.
MIROKU: Dakki is cracking!
-It couldn't absorb all of
Tetsusaiga's demonic energy.
-Huh?
Tetsusaiga?
-It's reverted back
to its original form!
-It's exactly as
Totosai forewarned.
-Now what happens?
-Sango?
Let's go.
-No.
You guys stay out of this.
Tetsusaiga and I need to
finish what we started.
-That's fine with me.
Now that Tetsusaiga
is dead and gone,
you shall be the next to
serve as fodder for Dakki.
-No, Toshu.
You see, Tetsusaiga and
I are one in the same.
So long as I'm still alive,
Tetsusaiga will never die!
-This is suicide!
-Then I shall finish you off!
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
Tetsusaiga, I
won't waste the
path you've opened.
Dammit.
-Ha ha ha!
I've won!
[scream]
KAGOME: Inuyasha!
-Huh?
-Look at that.
Toshu's hand is completely
fused with Dakki.
-I can only presume that
Dakki was afraid of breaking,
and thus transferred the damage
from Tetsusaiga's attacks
directly to Toshu instead.
-(VOICEOVER) Idiot.
In the end, it was his
own sword that killed him.
SHIPPO: Tetusaiga is
back to normal now!
-You've done it, master.
Tetsusaiga now
has dragon scales.
Not that I ever doubted
you for an instant.
My faith in you has--
-Sure you did.
(VOICEOVER) Sorry to push
you so hard, old friend.
But you did well, Tetsusaiga.
MAN: Koga!
-Hm?
INUYASHA: It's those
two scrawny wolf boys.
-I can sense three
Shikon jewel shards
in the direction
they're heading.
No.
Four jewel shards.
-Well, Koga has two shards.
Who do the other two belong to?
-Could It be Kohaku?
-It doesn't feel like him.
I don't know where
these two are from.
-Well, there's only one
way to find out, right?
-I concur.
-Shinta!
Huh?
-Moryomaru.
-Koga.
What good fortune.
I thought I'd have to
come looking for you.
-You've changed quite a bit
since the last time I saw you.
-Help me!
Get me outta here, Kai!
-Hang in there, Shinta!
I'm coming to save you.
-No you're not.
You don't stand a chance
against this thing, kid.
-Does that mean you're
going to help us?
-Oh, I'll help.
In fact, I've been
waiting for a chance
to use the Goraishi
on this thing.
-Hm.
I shall absorb you and
your Shikon jewel shards.
-(VOICEOVER) Damn!
Shards couldn't have picked
a worse time to act up.
-Let's see how
you like Raimeiho!
-Goraishi!
-What's wrong?
You seem a bit sluggish
compared to the last time.
-Shut up.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
-Let's put that to
the test, shall we?
Prepare to be incinerated.
-Are you OK?
-Don't worry about me.
Worry about yourself.
-Ah.
It would appear
the child has also
brought me a Shikon jewel shard.
Now to you, Koga.
I'll be taking your shards next.
-(VOICEOVER) My
legs feel so heavy.
INUYASHA: Wind Scar!
What are you doing
here anyway, pup?
Moryomaru, you
swallowed something
that didn't belong to
you again, didn't you?
-Ha!
I'll have you know this
shell is invincible.
Nothing can reach my heart,
not even an army of soldiers.
-Is that a fact?
Well, can an army
of soldiers do this?
Adamant Barrage!
-Your Adamant Barrage.
That will be a great
addition to my arsenal.
-What were you
thinking, you moron?
-Last time I checked,
I was saving your neck.
Now get out of here!
-I have this feeling that
Koga's jewel shards are
being controlled
by Midoriko's will.
-Inuyasha!
-You have to save Koga!
-That's what I'm doing.
You've got something
that belongs to me.
And there's no way
in hell I'm going
to let you use my Adamant Spears
to crush scrawny wolf boy.
-Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga.
-He's gonna use it already?
-Huh?
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER) What?
Tetsusaiga's heating up!
-Inuyasha!
-I'm fine.
-Impossible.
How did you absorb
my demonic energy?
-Now to finish it.
-Inuyasha won't last much
longer, while Moryomaru
has vast amounts
of demonic energy.
-Then what's he doing?
If he keeps up like
this, he's going
to end up being consumed
the way Toshu was.
-Inuyasha, the arm that has
your Adamant Spears-- there's
a Shikon jewel shard in there.
-You see that?
-It's deep within his shell.
I don't know if my
arrow can reach it.
INUYASHA: Just mark the
spot so I know where it is.
-A futile effort.
Huh?
What?
-His arm!
-It opened up!
-You'll pay for making
me look like a fool.
Goraishi!
MORYOMARU: (VOICEOVER)
The wound that Sesshomaru
gave me is reopening!
-Can you move now, wolf boy?
-Yeah.
What choice do I have?
-Good. 'Cause I'm not planning
to wait around for you.
You got that?
-Yeah, well, right back at you.
INUYASHA: Come on,
Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga!
-One more time, Goraishi!
-No! ow can this be?
-Nice work, pup.
Now, I want you to attack
the same spot as last time,
then I'll deliver
the finishing blow.
-Don't you get carried
away, wolf boy.
-Bring it on, pup.
-You didn't look so
tough when Moryomaru
had you strung up by your legs.
-I don't remember
asking for help!
-You're both strong!
-He's right.
You're both strong.
-Just get it over with
and work together!
-In situations
like these, someone
needs to be the bigger man.
-Take this!
[shouting]
INUYASHA: (VOICEOVER)
My hands are burning.
I can barely hold onto
Tetsusaiga anymore.
It's like I can feel the
demonic energy passing
through the blade.
Gonna finish you!
Ah!
-You OK, pup?
Dammit.
He got away.
-Inuyasha!
Hang in there.
Huh?
Who are you?
-I am Byakuya.
Byakuya of the dreams.
I must say, that Dragon Scale
Tetsusaiga is most impressive.
Even Moryomaru had to run away
with his tail between his legs.
Although I assure
you, it would've
been Inuyasha running if
there had been one more of us
involved.
-You mean if you'd
been involved.
Is that what you're saying?
-Not another step!
I won't let you touch Inuyasha.
-You misunderstand me.
My role is merely to
observe, nothing more.
At least for the time being.
So long.
-That one sure gives
me the creeps, dammit.
-Koga, do you know
who that guy is?
-The latest
incarnation of Naraku.
-I thought so.
Inuyasha!
Pull yourself together.
-(VOICEOVER) Tetsusaiga.
I don't understand.
What happened to you?
-I watched the entire spectacle
from the sidelines, as ordered.
-Imagine that.
A sword that injures its
user with every swing.
Fascinating.
-Are you sure I shouldn't have
just finished him off myself?
Or perhaps you would
rather have him
use that sword to
kill Moryomaru?
-Will Inuyasha be
destroyed by his own sword,
his beloved Tetsusaiga?
Or will he manage to find
Moryomaru and kill him first?
I can't wait to find out.
[theme music]
KAGOME: Moryomaru
attacks Kinka and Ginka.
Then Sesshomaru faces
off against Moryomaru.
Meanwhile, we find
a way for Inuyasha
to cope with
Tetsusaiga's new ability
to absorb demonic energy.
-The Great Holy Demon Spirit?
-He's the demon equivalent
of a wise old hermit.
If you Always to master the
Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga,
you have no choice but
to train under him.
INUYASHA: Next time on
Inuyasha, The Final Act,
The Great Holy
Demon Spirit's Test.
-I'll train you well, Inuyasha.