[music playing]
-Hm.
Huh?
-What?
A Meido.
Kagome!
-Inuyasha!
Inuyasha!
-The well.
What happened to the
Bone Eater's Well?
-She's right.
It's disappeared.
Meido Zangetsuha!
Of course, the Shikon
jewel was afraid of Kagome.
SHIKON JEWEL: Kagome, you never
belonged in the Feudal era.
Return.
Return to the world
where you belong.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): If
I wish to return, I can?
-Kagome!
Don't you make any wishes.
Kagome!
"Toward Tomorrow."
MIROKU: Shippo.
Let us take over, Shippo.
Your health will suffer if
you don't get some rest.
-What happened to them?
Where did they go?
-With Naraku gone, I
thought it'd be over,
but it seems I was wrong.
Our fate remains tied
to the Shikon jewel.
-What?
A human?
-That is the priestess who
created the Shikon jewel.
-So that was Midoriko?
-She has been locked in battle
with us for hundreds of years,
ever since the jewel was born.
And Kagome will
suffer the same fate.
-There's no way I'm
going to let that happen.
Huh?
Naraku?
You're still alive?
-He's dead, but soon, he
shall come back to life
when Kagome gives into
her fear of the darkness
and falls prey to the
trap set by the jewel.
Naraku will awaken, and
a new battle of the souls
will begin within the
Shikon jewel, a battle that
will continue forever
from the very moment
that the Shikon jewel
was first transported
through time to the Feudal era.
From the beginning, this
has been Kagome's fate.
-So that's why the Shikon jewel
brought Kagome and Naraku here?
It wants their souls to fight
each other for all eternity?
-Kagome was born to
become part of the jewel
and fight within it.
That is the point
of her existence.
-You're wrong.
That's not why Kagome
was born, and I'm
going to prove it to you.
Kagome taught me how to smile.
More than that, she taught
me how to believe in people.
Kagome was the reason I was
able to make friends and rely
on those friends, to
shed tears for others,
to understand the meaning of
true strength and kindness.
Those are all things
Kagome taught me.
So this, this can't be her fate.
Kagome came into this
world to be with me,
and I was born for her as well.
SHIKON JEWEL: You're not
going to make a wish?
So you're choosing eternal
solitude in this darkness
instead.
-I'm coming.
Can you hear my voice?
Kagome, can you hear me?
Kagome!
-Inuyasha?
INUYASHA: Kagome!
-I can hear Inuyasha's voice.
-Don't make any wishes.
Promise me you won't.
Just hold on till I get there.
-Inuyasha!
I can hear your voice.
-Do you wish to see Inuyasha?
Answer me, Kagome.
Do you wish to see him?
KAGOME: Just like Kikyo.
She wished to see
Inuyasha again.
And even Naraku.
I'm sure his wish
was a modest one too.
What they didn't know is
that the Shikon jewel never
grants your real wish.
-Then what will you do?
-It is as we've told you.
There is only one way for
the two of you to meet again.
And that is for Kagome
to wish upon the jewel
and be trapped within it
as a fallen priestess.
You've made it
worse, half-demon.
For the sound of your voice has
only given Kagome false hope.
-What?
DEMON: Now, she will
undoubtedly make a wish.
Inuyasha, I want
to see you again.
-Kagome!
-We will not let her
hear your voice again.
-Shut up!
-Kagome!
SHIKON JEWEL: Be true
to your heart, Kagome.
You want to see Inuyasha.
Wish it, and it shall be so.
-Is that the one and
only correct wish?
-It is said that in the
end when the person who
obtains the Shikon jewel makes
the one and only correct wish,
the jewel will be purified
and disappear from this world
forever.
The one and only correct wish.
I just figured it out.
I understand now.
-Where are you?
Kagome!
What is this?
I can't see a way out.
Inuyasha has always come for me.
I've made my choice.
I have no wish.
Inuyasha will come for me.
I believe in him.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Meido Tessaiga.
Are you telling me that's
where I'm supposed to cut?
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
It'll be fine.
I believe in you, Inuyasha.
-Meido Zangetsuha!
Kagome.
-Inuyasha.
It's not an illusion.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): Kagome.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Inuyasha,
I wanted to see you.
Shikon jewel, I'm
ready to make my wish.
If Inuyasha hadn't
come, I would have
given in to my fear
of the darkness.
I never would have
found the correct wish.
But now, with Inuyasha beside
me, I am not afraid anymore.
Shikon jewel, disappear forever.
-I feel so warm.
So this is how it
feels to be at peace.
-It's over now.
-Yeah.
It's over.
-Lady Kaede, hurry.
-Don't rush me, child.
-But the baby's coming soon.
-Where is the
master of the house?
-He had to go to work.
-Ah well, I guess it is
their third child after all.
That's right.
It has already been three years.
MIROKU: Not to worry, gentleman.
Soon your houses will
be rid of demons.
-But a whole bale of
rice for each charm.
-Oh, this is much too expensive.
-[gasp] He used three.
-Inuyasha, here it comes.
-Huh?
Tessaiga!
Man, you totally ripped
those people off.
You were always greedy, but
this is a whole new level.
-I have to take what
I can get, my friend.
I have a lot of expenses now.
-Speaking of which,
shouldn't your baby
be coming any moment now?
[baby crying]
KAEDE: There.
You did well, Sango.
-It's a healthy baby boy.
-That was such a fast delivery.
-Everyone OK?
-Hm.
-Come hold your son.
-I wonder how Kagome's
doing these days.
-Yes.
Three years is a long time.
I remember waiting
for three days
right in the spot where the
Bone Eater's Well had been.
Then there was that
pillar of light,
and the well just reappeared.
And there was Inuyasha
without Kagome.
-Kagome is safe.
-Do you think she returned
to the other world
that Inuyasha spoke of?
-Well, it's not something
he likes to talk about,
but he once told me, as
much as he needs her here,
there are others who need
her and love her as he does.
-I feel for him.
Inuyasha must be lonely.
MALE SPEAKER (ON
LOUDSPEAKER): Congratulations
to our new graduates.
GRADUATE: Kagome!
-Hey.
-Hi, Mrs. Higurashi.
-Congratulations, girls.
-We all got accepted
into University.
-My.
That's wonderful news.
-I want to become
an interpreter.
-News anchor for me.
-Well, try student
president first.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
It's been three years.
Three days after the well
disappeared, a pillar of light
emerged, and the Bone
Eater's Well was back
and Inuyashi and I back with it.
-Sis, you're back.
-Kagome!
-Mom.
-I was so worried about you.
-Inuyashi saved my life.
Inuyashi, thank you so--
-Huh?
-Inuyasha.
Since that day, the
well hasn't worked.
I can't see Inuyasha anymore.
INUYASHA: It was strange.
One minute I was there
in Kagome's world,
feeling so relieved.
KAEDE: And the next, you
found yourself back here.
-Yeah.
Just like that.
I remember how Kagome's
mother, brother, and grandpa
were crying.
When I saw that, I realized
I wasn't the only one who
cared about Kagome
and needed her.
-Inuyasha, I'm speechless.
When did you become
such an understanding
and caring person?
SHIPPO: Weird, huh?
-Oh, Shippo.
You were off taking the Fox
Demon Exam, were you not?
-I just got promoted.
-Inuyasha, you're still going to
the well once every three days,
aren't you?
-Every three days?
Your devotion is
quite remarkable.
-Ahh!
So sunny up here.
KAEDE (VOICEOVER): Yet
they still cannot meet.
Kagome was cast into this
world with the Shikon jewel
and cast from it the
moment it ceased to exist.
She came here to destroy
the Shikon jewel.
Though I wish it
were not so, it may
be that Kagome's role
in this world is over.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): Why
did the well stop working?
Was it because of
the feelings I had.
Did I do it?
When the Bone Eater's Well
disappeared and I was left
stranded alone in the darkness,
I felt so scared and sad.
What I didn't
realize at the time
was that I'd been in the
darkness for three whole days.
Poor Mom, Grandpa, and Sota.
With me gone, they felt as
scared and sad as I did.
I felt really bad about
what I put them through,
and I was just so
happy to be back here.
I felt so relieved.
And then the well closed.
Inuyasha, ever
since then, I can't
stop thinking that
maybe the reason I
went to the Feudal
era and the reason
the well stopped working after
the Shikon jewel disappeared
was that my job was
done and I'm meant
to spend the rest of my
life in this world, a world
without you.
But Inuyasha, I want to see you.
-Kagome?
What's wrong?
-Mom.
The sky.
-Hm.
-Mom, I-- I've been thinking.
-Kagome, I understand.
TWINS: Doggie, doggie.
-You make a good toy.
-Hey, would you do
something about the twins?
-Girls, leave his ears alone.
-I'm sorry, Inuyasha.
-All right, girls.
Go slay the fox.
-No way.
I didn't sign up for this.
-Oh, Shippo.
-We slayed you.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
This scent.
There's no mistake.
-Inuyasha, I'm so sorry.
Were you waiting here for me?
-Kagome, you idiot.
What have you been
doing all this time?
-Kogame!
-You made it back.
-It's been much
too long, Kagome.
-Miroku, Sango, Shippo,
it's good to see you.
-Hey.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): I'm back.
[theme music]
-So, uh, what movie
do you want to go see?
-Hey, Sota.
I hear your sister's pretty hot.
Is that true or what?
-You should introduce
us sometime.
-That would be hard to do.
She got married right
after high school.
-That's fast.
-She's married already?
-Oh hey, Grandpa.
How'd your check-up go?
-Ah, uric acid
levels, but that's it.
-Welcome home.
Dinner's ready.
Come on up.
-Later.
-Hey, Rukeichi.
You're working hard
today, my friend.
-Ha.
Just keeping up with you.
[twins singing]
KAGOME: A lot has changed
since I've been gone.
But I guess that's to be
expected after three years.
Shippo leaves the village
at least a few times a month
to continue his training to
become a full-fledged fox
demon.
Miroku and Sango have
a growing family,
and that keeps them busier
than fighting demons ever did.
And as for Sango's
little brother, Kohaku--
-Master Totosai.
-Ah hello, Kohaku.
I brought the weapon
you requested.
It's a bit heavy.
-Thanks, Totosai.
-Tell me.
Do you still go and visit
Sango and her brood from time
to time?
-No.
It's too crowded there.
KAGOME: He's training to become
a mighty demon slayer, so
that he can help those who
are troubled by demons.
And if you're wondering
about that old flea Myoga.
-Come on.
Come on.
I'm right here.
KAGOME: I've also heard rumors
that Koga and Ayame were
married and that now he's become
the chief of the Wolf Demon
Tribe.
-Miss Ayame, take
good care of Koga.
All right.
-Oh, she'll take care of him and
keep him on a nice short leash
too.
-Both of you better shut up if
you know what's good for you.
Don't think I won't
beat you down--
-Is this one medicinal too?
Jinenji and Lady Kaede
have been teaching
me a lot of new things.
I'm even helping them to
make antidotes and perform
exorcisms.
-You're taking this
stuff seriously, huh?
-Yep.
I need to hurry up and
get used to this world.
As for Rin, she's been living
with Kaede in the village.
I thought Sesshomaru
would take her with me.
-Well, Kaede told him that
first she needed practice living
with humans, so Rin could
make the choice herself.
-Oh look, Sesshomaru.
I see that Kagome has returned.
-Hm.
-Big brother!
[growl]
-That's weird.
He looked like he was annoyed.
Huh, you too.
-That just sounded really wrong.
OK.
-How dare she be
so disrespectful.
We must reprimand her
for such behavior.
-Shut your mouth,
or I'll kill you.
-My, my.
Has Sesshomaru brought
you another present?
-He brought me a new kimono.
KAGOME: As I live
in this world, I
know that things will
continue to change,
but I'm not worried
about the future.
I'm going to spend
every day with Inuyasha.
No matter what, now
I know the two of us
will be together as we
head toward tomorrow.
[theme music]