[theme music]
-Judging by the damage, this
must've been quite the battle.
Now then, rock children.
What happened here?
I want you to tell me
everything you saw and heard.
-To the underworld with you!
How long can you keep this up?
-My life won't be
taken by scum like you.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
In Pursuit of Naraku.
[sigh]
-Hey.
Uh, Master Jaken, where
did Lord Sesshumaru go?
He's been gone a while.
[sigh]
-It pains me to consider
how Lord Sesshomaru must
be feeling right now.
After painstakingly
training with Tenseiga,
he learns that it was
but a part of Tetsusaiga,
the sword bequeathed to
Inuyasha of all people.
I cannot be sure where
Lord Sesshomaru went.
Having said that, I've
got a pretty good idea.
-I've moved.
Well, that should do it.
What have you done to my home?
-Did you really think you
could escape, Totosai?
-No.
I figured you'd show up
here sooner or later.
-Hmph.
RIN (SINGING): Lord
Sesshomaru's late.
I wonder where he is.
-Will you shut up?
How many times do you
need to repeat that song?
-I'll sing one
about you instead.
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER):
What is this sensation?
-Hey, what's the matter, Kohaku?
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER): My Shikon
jewel shard is being defiled.
An evil presence is nearby.
Both of you, run!
-Kohaku.
It's been too long.
-Naraku!
-Well, Totosai, you've
known about this
from the very
beginning, haven't you?
-Of course I did.
After all, I was the one
who separated Tenseiga
from Tetsusaiga and forged
it into a weapon all
those years ago, Sesshomaru.
So what are you
going to do about it?
Kill me?
Hold on!
Now, let me guess, you
met Shishinki, right?
SHISHINKI: Now, then, I
presume the old man was
unable to control Meido
Zangetsuha after stealing it
from me, its rightful owner.
That is why he cast it
away from Tetsusaiga.
And so, that unwanted technique
the one Tetsusaiga had no use
for, was given to
your Tenseiga instead.
TOTOSAI: Look here, I don't
know what kind of nonsense
that troublemaker
Shishinki told you,
but you were able to master
Meido Zangetsuha in the end,
were you not?
Your father was
correct when he judged
that you would be able to do so.
You have lived up to
his every expectation.
-Totosai, do you
honestly believe
I haven't realied what the
next step in all of this is?
-Next step, you say?
-I've never known you to
be this careless, Kohaku.
-What do you want?
Have you come for my shard?
-Of course.
Why else would I be here?
Yours is the last one.
With it, the Shikon
jewel will be complete.
Kikyo, who once purified
and protected your shard,
is no longer around to help you.
I'm afraid there's nowhere
for you to run now.
-Kohaku!
[groaning]
-Kohaku, hurry!
Now's your chance!
-Tetsusaiga has the
ability to steal techniques
from the weapons of its foes.
Tenseiga, on the other
hand, has no such power.
-I pity you, Sesshomaru!
What your father did was cruel!
It was cruel, you hear?
-Both of us know that
Father's true intention
from the beginning was for me
to perfect Meido Zangetsuha,
but only so that
Tenseiga could then
be absorbed back into Tetsusiga.
That is the truth, isn't it?
-Ah-- wow, I'm impressed.
-Hm?
-You figured that out
all by yourself, huh?
Well, you are exactly right.
Are you disappointed?
-Huh.
I'd be disappointed if
Tetsusaiga could actually
cut me down.
But that shall never happen!
-Whoa there!
-Huh?
TOTOSAI: Say, Sesshomaru?
Why do you think your father
set up your swords this way
in the first place, huh?
Do you really believe
he favored Inuyasha,
and simply left with you
the short end of the stick,
so to speak?
Either way, your
thoughts are too
clouded right now
to see the truth.
As long as you remain
so narrowly focused
on the heirloom
Tetsusaiga, you will never
understand your
father's long term plan.
-Silence!
SESSHOMARU (VOICEOVER): What
was Father's long term plan?
TOTOSAI: Sesshomaru,
abandon these attachments.
Abandon your attachment
to the sword,
as well as your hatred
toward Inuyasha.
Once you do, you may very
well surpass your father.
-Hm.
-Wel, I thought
that was it for us.
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER):
What was that light?
Where did it come frmo?
The shard was defiled by
Naraku's mere presence,
but as soon as he
touched it, I could
feel a pure light
flowing into it.
Like it was being purified.
Was it her?
Could it have been
Lady Kikyo's power
protecting my shard from Naraku?
NARAKU (VOICEOVER): Kikyo.
This was your doing, wasn't it?
You planted a single speck
of purity in my Shikon jewel.
One point of light.
Somehow that was enough
to purify Kohaku's shard.
-Well, it looks like
we managed to get away.
-Didn't I tell you there
was nowhere for you to run?
-He doesn't give up!
-Kohaku, do you have any idea
what Kikwho was planning?
Shall I tell you?
It's true that she purified
your Shikon jewel shard,
but she didn't do it
to save your life.
She did it because
she wanted to plunge
that one remaining pure
shard into my Shikon jewel,
and purify me along with it.
-Aun, please go faster!
-Yes.
Even in death, that Kikyo is
still a threat to my existence.
KOHAKU (VIOCEOVER):
In other words,
my shard can still be used
as a weapon to defeat Naraku.
-Now, now, Kahoku,
don't get your hopes up.
I have ways of
retrieving the Shikon
jewel short without
even touching it.
[screaming]
-Fly lower!
-What does Naraku intend to do?
-He's going to try to cut off
my head and take it with him.
-What?
-Exactly.
I will take your head with
the shard still in your neck,
allowing me to slowly defile it.
-That's Naraku's miasma.
-I think Kohaku's there, too.
I think his Shikon jewel shard.
-Kohaku?
-Let's go.
-So, if Kohaku's there,
shouldn't Sesshomaru
be there, too?
-He was.
But I can't smell
Sesshomaru now.
He probably ditched
them and ran off.
-We need to hurry.
If his shard is taken,
Kohaku will surely die.
-You're right.
-My, imagine meeting you here.
-Is that Byakuya?
-Sorry, but I'm afraid this
is as far as you go right now.
Nothing personal.
Naraku's orders, you understand.
-We don't have time to
play games with you!
-Same here.
I don't intend to stay
any longer than I have to.
Just until Naraku is
finished with his business.
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER): The
shard is being defiled again.
-Hpmh.
Enough of this.
Wind Scar!
-Miasma!
-Everyone stay back.
I'm gonna use my Wind
Scar to blow away
the rest of this miasma.
-I don't think so.
-He's right.
You can't stop them
from producing miasma.
-Stand back, Inuyasha.
-Miroku!
-Wind Tunnel!
-You crazy monk.
Don't you realize
you'll never survives
if you suck in all this miasma?
Oh!
-Sango, now's your chance!
Go find Kohaku!
-Thanks, Kagome.
Let's go, Kirara.
-Prepare to die, Byakuya!
-Ready and waiting.
-Dammit.
-Miroku, are you in pain?
-No.
Let's go after Sango.
-Just so we're clear, the
monk's body hasn't recovered.
You understand that, right?
He merely can't feel the
pain from his wounds anymore.
The damage from
the miasma remains.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): I know.
Stupid Miroku.
He looks totally fine.
I guess he really can't
feel the pain anymore.
Still, the damage
from the miasma
must have spread just now.
JAKEN (VOICEOVER):
What should I do?
If I allow Rin to get mixed up
in this and she gets killed,
Lord Sesshomaru
will slaughter me!
-Listen, Master Jaken,
we have to split up.
Take Rin with you and
go someplace safe.
-Kohaku?
-What?
I couldn't.
Is that OK?
-No!
We can't, Master Jaken!
[laughter]
NARAKU: You're in no position to
be worrying about your friends.
-No!
-Kohaku!
[screaming]
-Rin, put this on, and don't
take it off, no matter what.
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER): The
shard is being defiled again.
I can feel it getting worse.
-Kohaku, are you OK?
-Get away!
Get away from here, Rin.
-Kohaku.
[laughter]
NARAKU: Are you scared, Kohaku?
Scared that my demonic
energy will manipulate you
into harming that girl?
Perhaps you're afraid you'll
lose control and kill her,
just like you killed
your father and comrades.
Do not be afraid.
You will no longer
have to suffer
when I am through with you.
-Kohaku!
[laughter]
-Naraku!
-Sister, it's you!
-Sango.
If you truly care
for your brother,
end his life, so that he
may finally rest in peace.
-Don't be ridiculous.
-Do you know not
understand, Sango?
Death is the only way to save
Kohaku's soul from its torment.
I want you to think about it.
Your brother managed to escape
my control and come to his
senses, yet you siblings
still cannot be together.
Why is that?
It's because Kohaku
is avoiding you.
You, his loving
and devoted sister.
But who can blame him?
After all, Sango,
you saw everything.
Every shameful act he committed.
Like it or not,
your very presence
reminds Kohaku of
his hateful past.
-Is that all you have to say?
-Hm?
-That Kohaku is avoiding me?
What's your point?
I knew that already.
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER): Sister.
-Naraku, Kohaku may have
been under your control,
but that doesn't
change the fact he
killed our father in cold blood.
I too relive that day
over and over again,
just as Kohaku must.
I know he feels anguish
and shame for what he did,
and that is exactly why
I will not let him die.
Until Kohaku can overcome
that pain, until he is free,
I will continue to
fight you, Naraku!
[laughter]
-Your resolve is admirable.
Though sadly, it won't
be of much use to you.
-The demonic energy
grows stronger!
-Hurry, Inuyasha.
I can feel Kohaku's shard
continuing to be defiled.
-Sister-- please,
get out of here.
-Kohaku!
-Sister--
-You're able to speak
while under the control
of my demonic energy.
How amusing.
With that jewel shard
in you, your body
will be under my
control, and yet you
shall remain conscious
of if the entire time.
-Damn you!
-What will you do, Sango?
How do you plan to save
your precious Kohaku now?
-Silence, Naraku!
I am sick of listening
to your nonsense!
-Sango!
-Come, now.
You don't actually expect to
defeat me with Hiraikotsu,
do you?
NARAKU (VOICEOVER): Impossible.
I am a mass of demonic energy.
I cannot be shattered
by the same energy.
No.
There is more than
just my demonic energy.
Something new.
An entirely different poison.
[groan] My body
isn't recovering!
-Yes!
Adamant Barrage!
[scream]
-Where are you going?
-Wind Tunnel!
-Dammit!
he got away.
-Hiraikotsu.
-Sango, are you all right?
-That was incredible, Sango.
It seems like Hiraikotsu is way
stronger than it was before.
-Yes.
I sure didn't expect that.
-Smells like the master
of potions' liquor.
-You're right.
-You forget that your Hiraikotsu
has been swimming around
in my herbs and poisons.
it will never be the
way it was, as you say.
However, it won't be evident
to you until you fight again.
When you do, don't be surprised
by how it may have changed.
SANGO (VOICEOVER): Hiraikotsu
can now draw in demonic energy
and shatter it.
-Thanks to you, I actually
stand a chance against Naraku.
JAKEN: Where's Rin?
is she OK?
-Hm?
Oh, hey, Jaken.
How'd you end up getting
stuck to my foot?
-Because you stepped on me!
-Kohaku, are you OK?
-Kohaku's unable to move.
-Kohaku?
KAGOME: It must be
because the Shikon jewel
shard has been defiled.
we need to purify it.
-That didn't exactly
go as planned, do it?
-Shut your mouth, Byakuya.
-OK, fine.
Hm?
What's this?
NARAKU: A remaining fragment
of the mirror demon.
A memento of Kanna.
I want you to go and
give it to Sesshomaru.
-To Sesshomaru?
-Yes, that's right.
What no one knows is that
Sesshomaru is but a pawn.
My pawn.
The time has come to make
Inuyasha and the others
aware of that.
-OK, how's that feel?
-Good It feels a lot better.
I might not be able to purify
it as well as Kikyo could.
-Kikyo's light.
-Huh?
-It happened when Naraku
tried to take my jewel shard.
I'm not sure why, but the minute
his tentacles made contact,
this pure light started
flowing into him.
-From Naraku's tentacles?
-It almost felt as though
Lady Kikyo was purifying me.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER):
Does that mean
Kikyo's power somehow entered
Naraku and remains there even
now?
KANNA (VOICEOVER): The
light will destroy Naraku.
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): The
image Kanna showed me
before she died.
It was the Shikon jewel.
It was defiled, but
in the center of it,
there was a light.
That must've been Kikyo's light!
-And so--
-Huh?
-Kohaku.
Are you suggesting you'd
be able to use your shard
to defeat Naraku?
-Well, I--
-Naraku said he was going
to take Kohaku's head.
He said once he did that, he
could slowly defile the shard.
-Rin!
-Well, you almost died, Kohaku!
-Don't listen to her.
Look, sister.
It's clear that my shard
can cause Naraku pain.
I know Lady Kikyo's
power is protecting me.
That's why--
INUYASHA: Stop your babbling.
-Inuyasha.
-Give me a break.
Why do we have to keep
tip toeing around him?
Sango.
Just tell it to him straight.
It's a pain in the butt when
he wanders off by himself,
isn't it?
-Inuyasha.
Sit, boy.
-Why?
-It wasn't Kohaku's
fault this time.
Sesshomaru left
them there alone,
so it was just Kohaku
and the little ones
around when he was attacked.
-The little ones, who
are you calling little?
-Well, your height, your
heart, your personality.
So many things about
you are little.
-No.
It's just as Inuyasha says.
This isn't the first
time it's happened.
Kohaku.
You know you're weak
of heart and strength.
That is why Naraku can
take advantage of you.
If you fight alone, you don't
stand a chance against him.
Please tell me you
understand that much.
-It's true.
You're right.
-I believe that Kikyo left
her power in your shard,
but I don't think she
wanted you to sacrifice it.
I think she'd want
you to treasure it.
Protect it like the
beautiful gift that it is.
-Yes.
You're right.
KOHAKU (VOICEOVER): Lady Kikyo.
-Heh.
What a joke.
They still end up babying him.
-Must be nice to have all
those girls fawning over you.
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): I
shouldn't be surprised.
The damage from the miasma
continues to spread.
Please-- let me hold
on until it's over.
[theme music]
RIN: I'm begging
you, Lord Sesshomaru!
Please don't listen
to what Naraku says!
KAGOME: Sesshomaru joins
in Naraku's scheme,
he takes Tetsusaiga's
demonic energy,
and strands Inuyasha on
the path to the underworld!
SESSHOMARU: Prove it, Inuyasha.
Prove that it is you who is the
rightful heir to Tetsusaiga.
That is all I ask.
INUYASHA: Next Time on
"Inuyasha, The Final Act."
True Air.
Come on, Tetsusaiga.
I believe in you!