[theme music]
-So this is the
demon tree Yomeiju.
-Yes.
As you can see, it's
no longer alive,
but it is said that
long ago, it was
capable of devouring both
humans and demons alike.
MAN: Then about 50 years
ago, an esteemed priestess
came and placed a seal on
it, rendering it harmless.
-Yet now, new buds
have have sprouted.
-Yes.
We fear it may awaken and
begin to consume again.
-Now I understand.
Indeed, your fears
are justified.
I shall restore the seal.
-Thank you so much.
-How can we rpay you?
-It happened only
a few days ago.
since then, we haven't
dared to go near the Yomeiju
for fear it would
devour us, too.
-There sure are a lot
of new leaves on it.
The seal hasn't been
weakened, yet the tree
is coming back to life.
That can only mean one thing.
KAGOME: A Shikon jewel shard.
-What?
Really?
-It must be Naraku.
-Hmph.
I don't know what
Naraku's up to,
but he sure has been generous
in spreading these Shikon jewel
shards around lately.
They're everywhere.
-Indeed, they are.
But what use could he
possibly have for this tree?
-That won't matter
once I cut it down.
Wind Scar!
A barrier?
-I see you're still up to
your old tricks, Inuyasha.
-Naraku.
-I haven't tasted demon in ages.
-Go ahead, try to cut me down.
You won't get a
better opportunity.
But of course, my
heart isn't here
with me at the
moment, so I'm not
sure it would really
do you much good.
-It can fly!
-Not quite.
I believe Naraku's
taking it with him.
-You see that?
That bastard just
absorbed Yomeiju.
-Why'd he run away?
-He didn't come here to face us.
He came for the tree.
It doesn't make sense.
What could Naraku
want with Yomeiju?
There must be an explanation.
-Hmph.
Let's go
-(VOICEOVER) There's
no mistaking it.
That's Moryomaru's scent.
Huh?
It's that woman.
-What is it, Lady Kikyo?
-Kohaku, I can sense that
we're in the presence
of another Shikon
jewel shard bearer.
[rumbling]
-Lady Kikyo!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
The End of Moryomaru.
-I guess I got here too late.
No one could survive
a fall like that.
KIKYO: Your name
is Koga, is it not?
Have you also come here
in search of Moryomaru?
-Yeah, I have.
You too, right?
-Listen to me.
Cease your pursuit of Moryomaru.
-Lady.
I heard you were
reckless, not stupid.
-I've no intention
of taking your life.
I need only for you to
give me the Shikon jewel
shards in your legs.
-All right.
Now I'm sure you're insane.
You must have noticed by now.
Those Shikon jewel
shards in your legs
are being controlled
by the will of another.
I'm sure you've experienced
the sensation many times
now, where your legs stop
moving in the face of an enemy.
KOGA: Kagome told me about it.
She says it's happening because
of an ancient priestess called
Midoriko.
-And now I have joined
her soul with mine
for the sake of
defeating Naraku.
In order to destroy
him, the Shikon jewel
must be completed and
purified as a whole.
Every time your
legs stop moving,
it is because
Midoriko is attempting
to give your shards to Naraku.
However, if you lose your
shards in the midst of battle,
you may very well lose
your life as well.
-Oh, I see.
So you were hoping I'd just hand
over my shards and run away,
were you?
-I made a vow to bury Naraku.
You have my word.
-Don't give me that.
You listen to me.
You're not the only one with
a score to settle with Naraku.
He's killed dozens--
no, hundreds
of my fellow wolf
demon tribe members.
And still you expect me to
run away just to save myself?
Guess you were
ariming for my legs.
Big mistake.
Well, it's been interesting, but
if I waste anymore time here,
I may never catch
up with Moryomaru.
See ya, Kikyo.
-Lady Kikyo.
-I tried to prevent an
unnecessary sacrifice,
but I failed.
-Moryomaru is getting away.
We should go, quickly.
-Yes.
-The smell makes me sick.
-Naraku's demonic presence.
-We're getting closer.
-I've never seen a
miasma like this.
-They caused this?
-Don't get to close to it.
-I've been expecting you Naraku.
-So, Moryomaru, you long
for my Shikon jewel shards.
I applaud your ambition.
-Ha.
At this point, the only
advantage you have over me
is the number of
shards you pssess.
-It's futile.
I cannot be killed no matter
how many times you try.
My heart is inside
you, and I don't
imagine you want any
harm to come to it.
-Perhaps, but that works
both ways, doesn't it?
For you can not kill
me either so long
as your heart remains
inside my body.
-That's right.
Like it or not, our fates
are connected, Naraku.
If I die, you die.
-Really?
Before you go on,
I should tell you
that your betrayal
comes as no surprise.
I knew this would
happen when I first
released you from my body.
-What?
-You knew this would happen?
-Why would I allow my
heart, my very life
to exist outside my own body
in such a weak, infantile form?
Perhaps it is because
I know you so well
and I could see you
betraying me and attempting
to overthrow me one day.
And just as I expected,
to protect yourself,
you created a suit of
armor in Moryomaru.
Suit of armor.
No, he's a genuine fortress.
I must say you've done an
impressive job of fatenning him
up for me.
I look forward to devouring him.
-Hm.
You can not talk
your way out of this.
-You really think
you can defeat me?
Let us find out, shall we?
And may the one who's left
standing be vindicated!
-Lady Kikyo.
An enormous demonic
presence is rising.
-Indeed.
It would appear that
Moryomaru is not alone.
-You mean Naraku is there too?
-Hm.
-What's wrong, Naraku?
You have no better strategy
for beseiging this fortress?
-That's enough, Moryomaru.
He is but an empty shell.
Give him his last rites.
-It's over.
Die!
[groaning]
-I've consumed him.
At last, I've won!
-The jewel shards.
-Naraku's and
Moryomaru's jewel shards
are joining together now.
-All I need to do now is
obtain the remaining shards.
-The remaining shards?
Koga and Kohaku
are both close by!
-I have to admit, I
didn't think you had it
in you to beat Naraku.
-What's he doing here?
-No, Koga!
Run before it's too late!
-Don't worry about me, Kagome.
He's going to come
for me either way,
so I might as well face him now.
-How admirable of you.
-Goraishi!
I can't deflect 'em!
-Heh, heh.
Give up now.
-Adamant Barrage!
-Your attacks cannot
penetrate my armor.
-Run, scrawny wolf boy.
I need you to lure him
down to the ground.
-Huh?
-We don't stand a chance against
him while he's up in the air.
But on the ground, I can use
the Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga
to cut through his demon vortex.
-Hurry up, Inuyasha.
You and Koga need
to do something
before Moryomaru completely
absorbs the Shikon jewel.
-See?
Now get running.
-Easy for you to say.
I don't like this one bit.
-Let's go!
-I'm gonna leave you behind
if you don't speed up!
-We must go after them.
-Let's go, Kirara.
-Sango, I can sense
another shard.
That means Kohaku
must be nearby.
-Kohaku?
KAGOME: He's
probably with Kikyo.
SANGO (VOICEOVER): That's r
If Koga's shards are taken,
Kikyo will use Kohaku's shard.
If that happens, I'll
lose him forever.
-Let's get moving, Sango.
-Mm-hm.
-You can't keep up with me even
after swallowing the Shikon
jewel?
-You left yourself wide open.
Dragon Scale Tetsusaiga!
(VOICEOVER) I can't
see any demon vortices.
The demonic energy
is flowing back out!
-What are you doing, pup?
You were supposed to finish him!
-Shut up and keep moving!
-Forget it!
It's obvious I
can't count on you!
[laughter]
-Huh?
-Goraishi!
It didn't work!
-This won't be like
our last encounter.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): Damn.
I can't see any demon vortices.
The infant's Fuyoheki
must be hiding them.
-Out of my way, pup!
-Huh?
Hit him right here!
Get outta here!
-What the hell was that for?
-I said run.
This is all pointless
if you get caught.
-Huh?
(VOICEOVER) Dammit,
my legs won't move.
-No!
Koga!
-Moryomaru has
Koga's shards now.
We must hurry, Kohaku.
KAGOME: Wait!
Kikyo!
-Kohaku.
-Hello, sister.
-Kikyo, you intend to use
Kohaku's jewel shard, right?
-Kohaku-- please, there
must be another way.
You don't have to do this.
-It's OK.
I've made up my mind.
-It's the only way to destroy
the Shikon jewel and Naraku.
I hope you can forgive me.
-But he's my brother.
You can expect me to
just watch him die.
-Sister, this is the
path that I have chosen.
-That may be true, but
I still can't accept it.
-Stand aside.
We have no time.
-I can't do that.
If you insist, then you'll
have to go through me first.
-Sango, please--
-Kagome, I know you
can sense it, too.
Even as we speak,
Koga's shards are
being drawn into
the Shikon jewel.
-And that's why we're here.
Please, Kikyo, just wait
a little while longer.
-Waiting is not going
to change anything.
-Inuyasha has been doing
everything in his power
to make himself
stronger, because he
wants to defeat
Naraku before you do.
That way, innocent lives
don't have to be sacrificed.
-Naraku cannot be defeated
by the sword alone.
-Inuyasha's efforts have
to count for something,
don't they?
Whatever it takes, I'll
protect Koga's shards.
I promise.
Just give me some time.
Please, don't use
Kohaku's shard.
Not yet.
Sango, I need you to
stay here with Kohaku.
-Kagome, please, wait!
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): Kagome.
What can you possibly do?
KAGOME (VOICEOVER): I
believe in you, Inuyasha.
Don't let me down.
-Hey, scrawny wolf boy!
Don't go passing out on me, OK?
-Not a chance!
-Good.
'Cause I know how
we can win this.
I want you to listen up.
-Huh?
-Hm.
It's over.
I shall swallow you along
with your jewel shards.
-You ready?
I need you to use
the Goraishi on me.
-Sounds crazy to me,
but whatever you say.
Goraishi!
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER):
Neither Koga nor I
can break through
that shell on our own.
But together--
-Tetsusaiga's absorbing the
Goraishi's demonic energy!
-I see.
He's trying to combine the
demonic energy of both weapons.
-Now we have twice the power!
-It's no use.
My demon vortex is
hidden by the Fuyoheki.
-I don't need any demon vortex.
The part of you that's
trying to suck in Koga
leads straight to your
insides, you bastard.
-Damn you!
-It's miasma!
(VOICEOVER) I can't breathe!
-Get up.
What the hell are you doing?
-Huh?
-Inuyasha!
-It didn't want, Kagome!
-How dare you?
-Come o let's go.
-Right.
Let's finish him off.
What is it, Kagome?
What's wrong?
KAGOME: Moryomaru hasn't
absorbed the Shikon jewel yet.
-What?
Are you sure?
-Yes.
I don't know what he's waiting
for, but I can still see it.
-What is it?
My armor should be
invincible after consuming
Naraku and the Shikon jewel.
But the jewel's powers don't
seem to be having any effect.
NARAKU: You still haven't
figured it out, have you?
[gasp]
-Moryomaru is still
vulnerable because he's
unable to use the power
of the Shikon jewel.
-Naraku.
So you were alive all this time?
-Foolish creature.
Never realized that you were
being consumed from within.
-Dammit!
My legs are stuck.
Even if you do consume
Moryomaru from the inside,
you'll never break
through my barrier.
(VOICEOVER) What?
How are they getting through?
-These tendrils belonged to a
demon tree known as Yomeiju.
It dissolves barriers
to feast on demons.
I had this specially
prepared just for you.
You'd be wise to accept
it and return to my body.
-Damn you.
I'd rather die than
be consumed by you.
-Look at that!
-The infant's coming out?
-Get down.
Adamant Barage!
NARAKU: You would abandon
Moryomaru in order
to escape from me, would you?
Despite knowing
that the minute you
step outside of his
protection, you will be killed.
-But when that happens,
you too shall die.
-Spiteful child.
You'd actually
sacrifice yourself just
to take me with you?
-You little bastard.
Goraishi!
-Hold on, Koga!
-Kagome--
-As usual their timing
couldn't be worse.
-Kirara!
-Ah!
Kagome!
Moryomaru, you bastard!
-Oh, but Moryomaru
no longer exists.
[gasp]
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): Naraku.
You actually survived?
-This is the end.
-What just happened there?
-I think he's
absorbing the infant.
MOYROMARU (VOICEOVER) Koga.
Your body sill soon dissolve,
and your jewel shards
will fall into my hands, at l
-Why can't I move?
-Please, lend me your strength.
-However, know that we
can only protect you once
from the power which
controls the Shikon jewel
shards in your legs.
The power which is not
a part of this world.
-Kirara, take me as
close to Koga as you can.
-Kagome!
-I'm sorry, but I
have to save Koga.
I promised Kikyo that I would.
-Huh?
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): The
souls of Koga's ancestors
are being overwhelmed by
Naraku's demonic presence.
-Almost there.
If I can purify that arm--
please let this work!
No!
I missed!
-Heh.
Pathetic.
Did you really think
you could save him?
Hm?
KOGA (VOICEOVER):
My legs are burning.
They move!
Naraku's heart.
The infant.
I'm OK.
They're protecting me.
-The infant!
[howling]
-Koga's alive!
-Hear that?
-The wolf demon tribe must
have been protecting him.
KIKYO (VOICEOVER): Kagome's
arrow lent its power
to the souls of his ancestors.
You!
Won't get away!
-Everyone, stand back!
Wind Tunnel!
-Damn you, monk.
-Naraku!
So I will sever the
ties that bind us!
-Miroku!
-It'll kill you!
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): I may
never get another chance
to destroy him.
-Please, you have to stop.
Stop before it's too late!
-I can't do that!
-The miasma's toxins will kill
you before you can suck me in.
-That would frighten me if I
were only doing it for myself.
But I'm not.
I'm doing this for
Sango, and Kohaku, too.
-No.
Miroku!
-If I can just hold
it a bit longer!
-Miroku!
-It's killing him!
-Curse you, monk.
You won't have my heart!
-Let go!
You've already lost!
-He sucked in the Fuyoheki!
-No!
I don't want you to die!
-Miroku.
That's enough.
-I see you're as naive
as ever, Inuyasha.
If you hadn't stopped him, he
would've sucked in my heart.
He had the perfect
opportunity to destroy me,
and you stopped him.
For that, I thank you.
-He-- He got away.
-Miroku!
Oh, no.
-Sango.
Forgive me.
-(VOICEOVER) Miruoku
did it for Sango.
That's why he wouldn't
close the wind tunnel.
He knew if he could
destroy Naraku,
Kikyo wouldn't have
to use Kohaku's shard.
KIKYO: The wounds
from the miasma
extend down his right arm,
like the legs of a spider.
If the wind tunnel had remained
open even a minute more,
he would not have survived it.
-Will he make it?
-I'll attempt to
purify him, but you
must understand, a body that's
taken that much miasma is
unlikely to ever
be fully restored.
-Please try.
-Help him, Kikyo.
-Oh, Miroku.
[theme music]
KAGOME: Byakuya of the dreams
is after Kohaku's jewel shard,
but when Sesshomaru appears,
his plans have to change.
Meanwhile, Kikyo clings
to life after being
caught in Naraku's web.
KIKYO: Naraku knows of my plan.
He knows that I
intend to purify him
and the Shikon jewel together.
KAGOME: To save
Kikyo, we must go
to the sacred
mountain, Mount Azusa.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"InuYasha, The Final Act."
The Mausoleum of Mount Azusa.
KAGOME: Why aren't we
getting any closer?
Is it because I have doubts?