[music playing]
[theme music]
-Found you.
[gasp] Rin!
-(THINKING) Miroku, you better
not open your wind tunnel.
-Miroku!
-Don't do it.!
-That's enough, Naraku!
Wind tunnel--
-Miroku!
I won't let you.
Kagome, the beads.
-Right.
(THINKING) I see
it, his real body.
This better work.
-Forgive me, Rin!
-Hmm?
-Huh?
-You tried to kill
her, didn't you,
along with the illusion of
Naraku that I created for you?
It's fitting, really, the demon
slayer Sango slays herself.
-I will not attempt to justify
it, or beg for my life.
But please, let me finish this.
Once the curse has been lifted
from Miroku, I'm all yours.
-[chuckling]
-His miasma!
-Damn it!
-Have you noticed
anything different?
This miasma is much more potent.
In fact, it is
deadly, especially
for weak humans like
Kagome and the monk.
-(THINKING) He's not
taking any chances.
You must be getting
desperate, Naraku.
-(THINKING) Naraku is
afraid of my arrow.
He doesn't want me to shoot.
-This won't be enough
to get rid of us.
Prepare yourself, Naraku.
I'm coming for you!
INUYASHA: Narku's
Uncertain Wish.
-Lord InuYasha!
-You'd better make it
out of there, InuYasha.
You have inherited Meido
Zangetsuha from your brother.
But now it is up to you to
make the technique your own.
Do that, and you can not lose.
-(THINKING) The miasma
is getting stronger.
-Lord Sesshomaru, please
catch up to Sango.
-Hmm.
-What?
-So he doesn't want us to
catch up to her, does he?
-(THINKING) Wait for me, Miroku.
-Whoa.
It'll take more than
that to defeat me.
Good.
I still have Genenges antidote.
As long as I take
this, I don't have
to be afraid of the miasma.
Only the three left.
That's OK.
I'll just go as far as I can.
-Damn.
Can't get a solid footing.
-Whoa!
-Don't worry.
I've got you, Kagome.
-Thank you.
Huh?
[wind howling]
-(THINKING) I can hear the
sound of Miroku's wind tunnel,
even when it's closed.
We don't have much time.
--[chuckling] InuYasha, as your
bitterness towards me grows
and gets stronger, so too does
the darkness within the Shikon
Jewel.
So struggle more,
suffer more, and lament
your own powerlessness.
-Naraku!
-Ah, Sango.
I've been waiting.
-Sango!
-(THINKING) Sango.
-(THINKING) Miroku, I found you.
-Sango, where is
your protective mask?
You won't be able to
survive the miasma.
-I'll shatter any miasma
or demonic energy.
Hiraikotsu.
-What's that?
-Miasma tornadoes.
-Have you've forgotten?
Hiraikotsu can shatter
your demonic energy.
-It worked.
-[labored breathing]
-Oh no!
NARAKU: It's too late for that.
Sango has already been
thoroughly exposed
to my miasma.
She should never
have given the mask,
her only means of
protection, to Rin.
It was a foolish
decision based on guilt.
And it will cost Sango her life.
-Sango!
Ah!
-Sango, Miroku!
Whoa.
InuYasha, we have to save them.
-Right.
--[chuckling] The least you
can do is allow them to spend
their last moments
alive in privacy.
-Sango!
Please, wake up, Sango.
Why?
Why did you do that?
[wind howling]
-(THINKING) I can still hear
it, Miroku's wind tunnel.
I, I failed, didn't I?
-Please forgive me
for abandoning you.
-Miroku?
Take me with you.
Promise me that
we'll die together.
-Sango.
-[chuckling]
-The hell is going on, Kagome?
-It's the Jewel.
It's been taken
over by darkness.
-The power of darkness feeds
off the monk and Sango's sorrow.
-Damn you, Naraku!
-Ironic, isn't it?
The stronger their
love is for each other,
the greater their despair.
The monk and Sango
will soon be no more.
They have chosen
to die together.
Even now, they wait for his wind
tunnel to swallow them both.
Do you understand, InuYasha?
The two of them will
soon be consumed
by the darkness of
the Shikon Jewel.
-I'm not going to
let that happen.
Naraku, I'll defeat
you here and now,
and lift the curse of
the wind tunnel for good.
Meido Zangetsuha!
-(THINKING) Naraku is joining
with the Shikon Jewel.
-He's not being sucked into it.
-Is that the power of the Jewel?
-All those years
ago, the Shikon Jewel
was supposed to have
burned with Kikyo's corpse,
and been obliterated
from this world.
Even so, the Shikon Jewel used
Kikyo's lingering feelings
for InuYasha, as well Kagome's,
her own reincarnation,
to return to this world.
Shattered but not
destroyed, the Jewel
continued to bring
new disaster, as it
slowly but surely reassembled.
The Shikon Jewel will never
disappear from this world.
Even if I am destroyed,
it will live on.
-(THINKING) Huh?
Naraku, what were-- what were
you even trying to accomplish?
-(THINKING) Huh?
Kagome?
-The whole time you've
been fighting against us,
it's always the same
thing, over and over again.
First, you tore Kikyo
and InuYasha apart,
forced Sango and Kohaku to
fight against each other.
And now you're trying to use the
love between Miroku and Sango
to destroy them.
You can't stand
love and friendship.
So you've devoted
your entire life
trying to break people apart.
But why?
Is that all you really wanted?
-Why ask me now?
-You couldn't have done
any of those things
if you didn't understand
the human heart.
The pain of loss wouldn't
mean anything to you
if you didn't know
what if it felt
like to have a
bond with someone.
-(THINKING) Kagome,
what are you doing?
-Nothing will ever satisfy you,
because the Shikon Jewel didn't
grant your real wish.
-(THINKING) This woman.
-You were hesitating,
weren't you?
Because you know
the Shikon Jewel
turns every body that it
absorbs into a true monster.
-(THINKING) My hesitation.
-You have a complete
Shikon Jewel in your hands.
And yet we both know you still
haven't tried to absorb it.
-That changes nothing.
Are you so naive
that you think you
can purify my heart
with your empty words?
Well, you are sadly mistaken!
-Kagome, stand back!
Meido Zangetsuha!
Naraku!
You and I may be nothing alike.
But we are both half demons.
That means that in
both of us there
is a human heart and
a demon heart, Naraku.
But you have betrayed that.
We were both given
the freedom to choose,
to follow our human
heart or our demon heart.
And you chose to
live as a demon,
ignoring all that
was human in you.
You chose to hurt
others, and curse them
with misery and suffering.
But your days of
hurting my friends
are over, you miserable bastard!
-Huh?
-(THINKING) Meido took
the form of blades.
-(THINKING) Impossible.
My tentacles are gone!
-So Meido Zangetsuha
has evolved.
-Wonderful!
Does this mean that
the technique now
truly belongs to
Master InuYasha?
-Yes.
As you know, Meido
Zangetsuha was first
achieved using
Sesshomaru's Tessaiga,
a sword that can not cut.
Thus, the original method
of opening the Meido
and sending foes to their death
was best suited to that sword.
-So the fact that InuYasha
was able to produce this new
Meido--
-InuYasha's sword and technique
have finally united as one.
-Yes?
-Miedo has taken
the form of a blade.
-Yes?
-And that is a reflection
of InuYasha's Tessaiga.
-Oh, yes.
-The Shikon Jewel?
If I can just pierce it.
(THINKING) If I can
pierce the Shikon Jewel,
Naraku will be destroyed.
Ah!
-Kagome!
-It's futile.
Attack me all you like.
But you are still inside
my body, you fool.
I'll only keep regenerating.
-Fine by me.
I'll keep slicing
you up all day.
Naraku, I'm going to sever
you from those tentacles,
and every other attachment
you ever had to this world,
and that includes any ties
you still have to the Jewel.
Prepare yourself.
Meido Zangetsuha!
-Damn you, InuYasha!
-Ah!
-(THINKING) No.
If Sango's exposed to any more
miasma, she won't survive.
SANGO'S VOICE: Promise me
that we'll die together.
-You can't die.
I won't let you!
You are going to
survive this, Sango!
-What now?
Ah!
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
It's miasma.
I never should have come
here in the first place.
I'm so alone!
-(THINKING) Utter nonsense.
The Shikon Jewel didn't
grant my real wish.
InuYasha thinks he
and I are the same.
How dare you?
-Lord Sesshomaru,
there's so much miasma.
-(THINKING) It seems
you've reached the point
of desperation, Naraku.
In that case, I shall
perform your last rites.
Bakusaiga!
-Amazing!
-A path has opened.
-Only Bakusaiga could do this.
The damage will
continue to spread.
Any piece of flesh it
touches will be destroyed,
and will in turn
destroy all that it
comes into contact with.
Well, then.
It would seem the
time has finally
come for me to fulfill my role.
-What is it this time?
[screaming] Lord Sesshomaru!
-Master Jaken, you came?
-What have you been
doing all this time?
-Many things.
-Are you OK, Kagome?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
Huh?
-Sesshomaru must
be getting closer.
-Then this sound--
-That must be Bakusaiga.
Naraku, your body can
no longer regenerate.
-It's just as I
told you, InuYasha.
You may destroy me,
but the Shikon Jewel
will never disappear
from this world.
-[coughing] It's a dead end.
Oh.
Should I use the wind tunnel?
Even if it tears open,
and I'm sucked into it,
I have to at least try
to save Sango's life.
I will not let her die here.
It's getting quieter.
Whoa!
-[panting]
-Oh no!
Naraku's breaking up.
Aw, man, it's getting closer.
I have to keep going, or
I'll get caught in that mess.
Huh?
Whoa!
Watch it Kirara.
[screaming]
-Incredible.
-That one swing sure
did a lot of damage.
-Naturally.
Lord Sesshomaru's Bakusaiga
is in a class unto itself.
-If you insist on struggling,
Naraku, Bakusaiga!
-Give it up, Naraku!
It's all over.
So it would seem.
However, InuYasha, I'm
afraid that there's still
one thing that not even you
Tessaiga or Sesshomaru's
Bakusaiga can cut.
-What?
Why don't you just
admit that you lost?
-[chuckling]
-Your soul, is that what
you're talking about?
I'm pretty sure
that's why I'm here.
I'm here to purify
your soul, Naraku!
-Hah. (THINKING) Give it
your best shot, Kagome.
This will end with a
battle between souls.
-It's Byakuya.
-Huh?
-[chuckling]
-Bastard!
-I am but an
incarnation of Naraku
that will die when he does.
I have no regrets.
I have fulfilled my role.
-Kagome!
-Are you OK?
-I think.
(THINKING) Did he cut me or not?
-(THINKING) The technique he
just used was Meido Zangetsuha.
But why?
What was he trying to do?
-[chuckling]
-[panting]
-Thank you so much, Shippo.
You're a true lifesaver.
-I a-am.
But are you sure
you want to give us
the rest of your antidote?
-Of course.
Don't worry about me.
Just hurry up and take it.
-Well, I very much
appreciate it.
Sango.
You're awake.
-I am, Miroku.
-Please try not to move
around, not until the antidote
I gave you starts
to take effect.
-It's a good thing that
I brought the antidote
that Genenge gave me, huh?
-Miroku, the antidote
won't be enough for you.
-There's hope.
Haven't you noticed?
You can barely hear anymore.
-You think?
-Yes, presumably
InuYasha and the others
have fatally wounded Naraku.
And the power of the
curse of the wind tunnel
has been weakened.
-In that case, we must
hurry, and join them.
-Indeed.
We shall settle this
Naraku once and for all.
-(THINKING) Naraku
is still alive.
What's taking you
so long, InuYasha?
-Kagome, get on!
There's nowhere left to stand.
It's time to end this.
Meido Zangetsuha!
Kagome, shoot!
-Whoa!
-Bastard's still
trying to resist.
-InuYasha, look out!
-Huh?
Sango, Miroku!
-Kagome!
-Shippo?
-What are you doing here?
-A thanks would be nice.
I came to help you guys.
-Wind tunnel!
-Miroku!
-It's OK.
I'm fine now.
The curse of the wind
tunnel is already fading.
-Sesshomaru?
-Sister.
-Sango!
-Kohaku, Rin!
-(THINKING) I'm so
glad sister is safe.
-Bakusaiga's destruction
is spreading!
I knew Lord Sesshomaru would
be the one to defeat Naraku.
-(THINKING) So you're all here.
You and your worthless
group of so-called friends.
-Yeah.
All of us, everyone survived.
[music playing]
The well has been sealed.
Kagome, there is
nowhere for you to go.
KAGOME: That is the
wish of the Shikon Jewel
that Naraku was forced to make.
I was drawn into the Meido.
But-- huh?
I'm in high school already?
Oh, grandpa, this is bad!
GRANDPA HIGURASHI: The
well has disappeared.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"InuYasha, The Final Act--
Thoughts Fall Short" Please,
Tessaiga, take me to Kagome!