[music playing]
[theme music]
-So you're all here, you
and your worthless group
of so-called friends.
-Yeah, all of us,
everyone survived.
INUYASHA: Thoughts Fall Short.
-Lady Kaede, what is that?
KAEDE: It's Naraku.
He's falling apart
-Wind tunnel!
-Hiraikotsu!
-Meido Zangetsuha!
-Bakusaiga!
-[chuckling]
-Naraku cut himself
free from his own body.
-He must be trying to escape
Bakusaiga's destruction.
-Escape?
A futile efforts.
KAGOME: (THINKING) There's
light within the jewel.
-What a simple bunch you are.
This little gathering of
friends has bought my back
to the Shikon Jewel yet again.
Was that what you hoped for?
Do you think you have won?
I assure you, you have not.
For the Jewel and I are now one.
-The darkness is
pushing out the light!
-Bastard.
So he finally fed his
soul to the jewel, did he?
-It's another mass of miasma.
-Meido Zangestuha!
Come on.
I keep hitting him.
But he just won't go down.
Well, I wasn't
expecting the Jewel
to leave this world
without a fight.
-More miasma!
-You're worthless.
Bakusaiga!
(THINKING) The miasma leaking
from his severed flesh
is stronger than it was before.
Jaken.
-Yes, my lord?
-Leave Naraku's body at once.
-At once? (THINKING) I've
been long awaiting that order.
-But--
-Silence, you fool.
Two children such as you
will only get in his way.
-Lord Sesshomaru.
-It's outside too.
SANGO: Hiraikotsu.
-Sister?
-Kohaku, get out quickly.
-Oh, Lady Sango, this is yours.
Thank you so much.
-You're welcome.
-Miroku, take this.
-Kohaku?
-Use it.
And take care o my sister.
-I will.
Let's go, Sango.
-Right.
-Wow.
This cloud of
miasma is enormous.
-It's the same size
as the first time
we saw it, only now it's
just a hollow shell.
-Oh, this is bad.
I think it's starting to fall.
And look where it's heading!
-Wind tunnel!
No matter how much I suck in,
more miasma keeps flowing out.
-Are you OK, Kagome?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
I don't know why, but
all the miasma around me
seems to have been purified.
(THINKING) Still,
Naraku interferes
every time I try to draw my bow.
If only I could get a shot off.
-(THINKING) I won't
let you shoot, not yet.
-Meido Zangetsuha!
-Bakusaiga!
-Just a little longer,
a little longer.
VILLAGER: We're doomed!
Lady Kaede!
-It' coming this way.
-All of you, flee to the forest.
-OK!
-(THINKING) Naraku and Onigumo
have a fated connection to this
village.
Of course!
He intends to destroy it.
-Meido Zangetsuha!
It's no use, Naraku.
You've lost.
No matter how much
you try to resist it,
your body's falling apart.
-Enough of my body
still remains, enough
to wipe out a single
village, at least.
-A village?
-Oh!
-The masses of miasma are
falling to the ground.
[screaming]
-Any exposure to the
miasma will be fatal.
You must get the young
ones out of here.
-Naraku, bastard.
-Don't tell me you didn't
realize where we were,
InuYasha.
[cackling] It's too late now.
If you kill me, my
miasma-laden corpse
will descend on the village,
destroying everything.
-And what of it?
Bakusaiga!
-He's fallinga apart.
-The Shikon Jewel
is still alive.
It's falling by Naraku's will!
Hey Shippo, can you
make it outside?
-Yeah.
-Sango, we should join them.
-Yes.
-(THINKING) It would appear
that not even Bakusaiga can cut
the Shikon Jewel.
-[screaming]
-Wind tunnel.
-Meido Zangetsuha!
-(THINKING) I see it!
This is my chance!
Believe in yourself, and shoot.
My arrow will pierce
the Shikon Jewel.
I know it will.
-The arrow disappeared.
-(THINKING) Please
pierce the Jewel.
Nothing will ever satisfy you.
Because the Shikon Jewel
didn't grant your real wish.
NARAKU: My real wish, you say?
That's right.
Now I remember.
All I wanted was Kikyo's heart.
It seems I won't
be joining Kikyo
in this or the next world.
-[gasp]
-Oh!
VILLAGER: Is it over?
VILLAGER: The masses of
miasma are disappearing.
VILLAGER: We're saved.
-The miasma around the
village is being purified.
-This must mean that Kagome's
arrow defeated Naraku.
-Did I do it?
[gasp]
-Huh?
Kagome!
-Kagome!
-InuYasha!
-Damn!
-[screaming]
-Damn it!
Naraku.
At that very moment,
I made a final wish
upon the Shikon Jewel.
-That moment?
NARAKU: The moment
Byakuya of the Dreams
cut you with his blade.
-Hang on.
She was cut by Byakuya?
-That wish shall be
granted when I die,
though it was not
mine to begin with.
The Shikon Jewel forced
me to make its wish.
In the end, I was
but its instrument.
-Naraku.
-[gasp]
-[gasp] Miroku!
-Has the wind
tunnel disappeared?
-The curse has been broken!
-It has indeed, which
means Naraku is no more.
-Hmm.
Huh?
-What?
A Meido?
Kagome!
-InuYasha!
InuYasha!
-The Meido vanished.
She's gone!
-(THINKING) What's going on?
Kagome?
-Um, was Kagome
really cut by Byakuya?
-Yeah, she was.
-Because I saw him,
inside Naraku's body.
He was stealing demonic energy
from the Meido Zangestuha.
-Huh?
KAEDE: The well.
-Yes, what about it?
-What happened to the
bone eater's well?
-Huh?
-She's right.
It's disappeared.
-Hey, Sota.
-What's going on?
Is Kagome still sick?
-I mean, can't she even make
it to our high school entrance
ceremony?
-Afraid not.
We're as worried as
you are, believe me.
-[sigh]
-(THINKING) I wonder
what happened to sis.
She said she'd back in time for
the entrance ceremony for sure.
[screaming]
-Was that an earthquake?
-I don't think so.
It felt like it came
from inside the shrine.
-Wait.
-Oh, wait up.
-Hey, you can't go in there!
-Maybe something broke inside.
Hmm?
-Huh?
Mom, grandpa, this is bad!
GRANDPA HIGURASHI: Ah!
The bone eater's
well has disappeared.
-(THINKING) Oh, Kagome!
-Maybe Kagome went home,
you know, to the world
on the other side of the well.
-I doubt it.
-The thing is, if Naraku
wanted to eliminate Kagome,
he could have done it long ago.
Instead, he was focused
on reaching this well
in this village.
What was it?
What was Naraku's final wish?
InuYasha!
-Huh?
-What happened to
the Shikon Jewel.
-(THINKING) The Shikon Jewel?
Please, Tessaiga,
take me to Kagome!
-InuYasha.
-Meido Zangetsuha!
-[gasp]
-(THINKING) Of course.
The Shikon Jewel was
afraid of Kagome.
At the very end, it would
have done anything to survive.
So there's no way it could
risk letting her live.
Hang in there, Kagome!
I'll find you, no
matter what it takes!
-One, two.
One, two.
-Oh, there she is!
Kagome!
-Huh?
Oh, hey guys.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
Come shopping with us.
-We need to get some sportswear.
KAGOME: (THINKING) That's right.
I almost forgot.
I'm in high school now.
KAGOME'S FRIEND: So
what did you tell him?
KAGOME'S FRIEND: That
I'm just not into him.
KAGOME'S FRIEND: What?
Why?
-But you guys are
perfect for each other.
-Yeah, right.
I can't date someone
who's shorter than me.
-Uh, OK.
-Huh, what's this?
Someone asked you out?
Who was it?
-Really?
The guy from the
entrance ceremony.
Don't you remember?
-Yeah, you were right
here with us, Kagome.
-Oh, right, him. (THINKING)
The entrance ceremony?
MAMA HIGURASHI: Kagome, can
you come give me a hand?
Have you decided on a
school club to join?
-I have, the tennis club.
Hey, uh, grandpa, how about
my real graduation present?
-Huh?
But I already gave it to you.
A dried dragon's tail and
tangu whiskers, for good luck.
Didn't you like them.
-Sorry, grandpa.
But I'm pretty sure
sis fed those to Buyo.
-They're dried foods.
-[gasp]
-Maybe you should
give her something
she'd appreciate next time.
COACH: All right,
freshmen, you ready?
Five laps, starting now.
-We bought all the gear.
-And we don't even get
to step on the court.
Huh?
-Wow, the archery club.
-That looks so cool.
-Hey, sis!
-Oh, Sota, welcome home.
-Man, I'm starving.
Uh, what's the matter, sis?
-Hey, was this shed always here?
-Yeah.
-Wasn't there, like, a shrine
here, with a well in it?
-What are you talking about?
-Oh, back from school already?
-Hi, grandpa.
-A shrine with a well?
-Yeah, don't think so.
There's never been
anything like that here.
-I could have sworn.
(THINKING) Why does
everything feel so weird?
What's wrong with me?
[phone vibrating]
Huh?
A message?
It's from Hojo.
HOJO: You want to go
see a movie this Sunday?
-(THINKING) I don't know.
What to do?
-Hey, Kagome, long time no see.
-So, are you getting
used to your new school?
What's a boy's
school like, anyway?
-I don't know.
There's a lot of guys.
-And?
-We went to the movies, and
then the arcade, ate some food,
and went home.
-So you decided to
go out with him.
KAGOME: No, we just hung out.
-But that was obviously
a date, Kagome?
KAGOME: We're just friends.
-You're just friends?
That is too cruel.
You do realize Hojo's
had a major crush on you
since junior high.
-Why don't you just go for it?
-It's not like you
hate him, right?
-No.
But it's just not
like that, all right?
-OK.
Is there someone else you like?
That, I could understand.
-No.
(THINKING) It's different.
there's supposed to be a
scar on the sacred tree.
A scar?
From what?
InuYasha?
That's right!
500 years ago, InuYasha
and I were under this tree!
The bone eater's
well has disappeared.
-Kagome!
-You there, sis?
-Mom, grandpa, Sota.
-Kagome!
-Huh, what's wrong?
-What are you doing, mom?
I'm here.
-What's wrong?
Mrs. Higurashi, what
happened to her?
-Huh?
-Is Kagome missing?
They don't see me.
No one sees I'm here.
-We were worried about her.
Because she hasn't made
it to high school yet.
And we know how hard
she worked to get in.
-[gasp]
SHIKON JEWEL: The
well has been sealed.
There is nowhere for you to go.
-It's the Shikon Jewel.
-Kagome, where are
you? (THINKING)
I have to keep searching.
She's got to be
somewhere in this Meido.
MAMA HIGURASHI: Kagome!
SOTA: Sis!
-Those voices, it's Kagome's
mom, and her brother.
Kagome isn't back on your side?
-Is that InuYasha
-Yeah.
That's his voice!
-Huh?
I don't--
-That sounds like--
-That was Kagome's boyfriend.
-The bone eater's well
has just disappeared.
What on earth
happened on that side?
-Do you know where Kagome is?
-Is sis OK?
Did someone hurt her?
INUYASHA: Try not to worry.
I promise you, I'm
going to find her.
Just hang on.
Kagome!
-Where am I?
What did you do to me?
-Kagome, you are where
you've been all along.
-That's impossible.
I was living at home.
I was going to high school.
SHIKON JEWEL: That was an
illusion, nothing more.
It was a glance at the future
that you might have had.
Do you wish to
return to that world?
It's not too late.
Wish upon the Shikon Jewel.
And the life you saw
shall be yours once more.
That, or do nothing.
And you shall spend
the rest of eternity
here, alone in the darkness.
-Out of my way.
[inaudible]
I tore that thing to pieces,
and it's already regenerating.
It doesn't make any sense.
-There's no need to search.
The priestess will
be here shortly.
-Priestess?
You mean Kagome?
-We can sense her
heart trembling
with fear in the darkness.
-Mom!
Grandpa!
Sota!
SHIKON JEWEL: No
one can hear you.
-InuYasha!
Miroku!
Sango!
Shippo.
-No one will come.
-It, it can't be.
-Soon she will give in
to a fear of darkness,
and wish upon the Shikon Jewel.
She will wish to be saved.
Already she longs to
escape the darkness,
and return to the peaceful
world she once knew.
-So then the Shikon Jewel
was never destroyed?
-Haven't you noticed, half
demon, where you are now
is inside the Shikon Jewel?
-Inside it?
-Yes.
And should Kagome
choose to save herself,
she will spend eternity
here, along with you.
-What?
-Once she is imprisoned
in the jewel,
she will be forced to do battle
against us for all eternity.
-There's no way I'm going
to let you imprison her.
-The Shikon Jewel will
never be destroyed.
The battle will continue
within the Jewel,
just as it always has,
until it is passed on
to another who will use
it for dark purposes.
It is a never ending cycle.
-Don't give in, Kagome.
Please, just hold on
until I get there.
-InuYasha.
SHIKON JEWEL: Kagome, you never
belonged in the feudal era.
Return, return to the
world where you belong.
-(THINKING) If I wish
to return, I can?
-Kagome, don't you
make any wishes!
Kagome!
[music playing]
-Lady Kaede, hurry!
The baby's about to be born.
KAEDE: Congratulations, girls.
-It's three years since that
final battle with the Shikon
Jewel.
I feel for him.
InuYasha must be lonely.
-I realized that I'm not the
only one who cares for Kagome.
Her family needs
her as much as I do.
KAGOME: But InuYasha,
I want to see you.
INUYASHA: Next time on
"InuYasha, The Final Act."
KAGOME: The final episode,
"Toward Tomorrow."
INUYASHA: Kagome came into
this world to be with me.