[music playing]
[theme music]
-Take this!
--[chuckling] The
arrow disappeared?
Huh?
-You are a true mystery.
-Huh?
-In the end, you
were able to combine
your own power and the
spiritual power of the bow
to shatter the evil
presence that bound me.
You saved me, Kagome.
That much I understand.
However, it was
only in the moment
you released the arrow that
your power became visible.
Something is sealing
your true power.
What it is, I do not know.
-What's the matter, Kagome.
You haven't said a
word since we left.
-It's nothing.
I'm fine.
(THINKING) If what Lady
Hitomiko said was true,
my power is being sealed
by something, or someone.
Kikyo, maybe?
Or perhaps--
Magatsuhi's evil will.
--[evil chuckle] Word
has spread, Sesshomaru.
-Rumor has it you've
lost your weapon.
-Lord Sesshomaru.
-Master Jaken, how come everyone
wants to fight Lord Sesshomaru?
-Honestly, these weaklings swarm
to challenge Lord Sesshomaru
in the hopes they can defeat
him now that he is weaponless.
For even that would
earn them prestige.
--[cackle] I've always wanted to
eat the flesh of a dog demon.
It looks like this is my chance.
-And once we defeat you,
the human boy will be ours.
-[gasp]
-Silence.
We're leaving.
-[gasp] Yes.
Wake up, Kohaku.
-Oh, right.
-I trust you understood, even
Lord Sesshomaru didn't quite
let them finish.
-Yes.
All of these demons have been
after my Shikon Jewel shard.
-Just knowing that, I shrink in
fear every time we're attacked.
-If you shrink anymore, you'll
disappear, Master Jaken.
-Like you're in any
position to talk.
-So Sesshomaru isn't
using his sword anymore.
I heard that InuYasha stole
that nasty Meido Zangetsuha
from him, and now
the sword at his side
is merely a dull piece of
junk that can't cut a thing.
Apparently what I heard is true.
I see.
So she's gone.
-I'm so sorry.
But I couldn't save her.
-InuYasha, you, too, have
suffered more than most.
-Well it's inevitable.
-Now, after many years of
great agony and suffering,
my sister's finally free.
-Yeah, I guess.
-We need to focus
on the present.
I'm afraid Kagome will have to
take on my sister's role all
by herself.
-But she can't.
Kagome's spiritual
power has been sealed?
-At least that's what
Hitomiko told her.
-And you believe my
sister's will is somehow
responsible for this?
-Well, that's what
Kagome believes, anyway.
-No.
That isn't possible.
My sister left everything
to Kagome, even her bow.
Why would she have
given her that,
if she were planning
to seal her powers?
-But who else could it be?
-I presume the
Shikon Jewel feared
Kagome's spiritual power,
and decided to take action.
-The Shikon Jewel?
-As you well know,
the Shikon Jewel
contains both a
good spirit we call
Naohi, and an evil
spirit, Magatsuhi.
If you are right about
Kagome's innate spiritual power
being sealed, there can
be but one explanation.
The evil will of the Jewel
sealed that power out of fear.
-Hmm, what's this?
-You must act now.
Mark my words.
If you continue
to stand by idly,
Midoriko will seize control.
And the evil we've put so
much effort into amassing
will be purified.
-(THINKING) That's
the Shikon Jewel.
What is Naraku doing?
-If it is flesh you
require, I will gladly
donate my own, manifest.
And then you can finally
eliminate the sacred light.
[grunting]
-That was strange.
What was that?
Naraku, was that a new
incarnation, or something?
-No, not quite.
It came from inside
the Shikon Jewel.
It is the evil will
of the demons that
have been sealed within
it for many years.
-Huh?
[gasp] What was that?
-Did you feel that
as well, Kagome?
-Yes.
I sensed something.
It was pure evil.
(THINKING) And I bet
it's coming to find us.
-Naraku's scent.
-Is something troubling
you, Lord Sesshomaru?
-Stand aside.
-Huh?
[screaming] What?
-Another incarnation?
Huh?
-[screaming]
-Kohaku, are you OK?
-I'm fine.
-(THINKING) Is this thing after
Kohaku's Jewel shard as well?
-You're weak, demon.
-What did you just say?
-I'll say it one more time.
You are weak.
-You got him, Lord Sesshomaru.
That insolent fool!
You do not call Lord
Sesshomaru weak,
unless you are very
brave, or very stupid.
Your loose tongue has
just condemned you.
-Now then, have you realized
how weak you are yet?
-Something's wrong.
-Why, Kohaku?
-Look at Lord Sesshomaru's arm.
When he attacked, it should
have pierced that thing's body.
But it looks like
it's being swallowed.
-Huh?
-Oh.
-Lord Sesshomaru's arm!
-What's this?
His venom is too
powerful for my Lord!
-[cackling]
-You must escape,
Lord Sesshomaru.
If you were to lose
your right arm,
you would no longer
be able to fight!
-Rinka, down.
-Huh?
-(THINKING) Fool.
-He's the Raku's incarnation.
So even if I attack
him, he can't touch me.
Because Lady Kikyo
purified my shard.
Ah!
(THINKING) What?
My shard is being defiled.
My shard!
-Lord Sesshomaru!
-That should stop you.
-Bastard!
-Kohaku!
Is he OK?
-Well, you must be
Naraku's latest.
-Naraku?
How dare you group me
with that half demon?
-Oh, Lord Sesshomaru,
such a tragedy.
-Sesshomaru doesn't look good.
-Passing Meido Zangetsuha
to InuYasha has cost him.
-Please, just be strong.
The shard's been defiled.
I'll purify it.
-(THINKING) Did
that guy defile it?
Is he just another one
of Naraku's incarnations?
Something feels
different about him.
[gasp]
-Kagome!
-What's wrong, Kagome?
-She just fell.
-All right.
What did you do to Kagome?
-[giggling maliciously]
-Take Kohaku and leave.
He's in the way.
-Huh?
-You too.
-Back off.
You're too badly injured.
You don't stand a
chance right now.
-Listen to this.
Whose fault do you think
this is the first place?
Since the day Lord
Sesshomaru generously
yielded Meido
Zangetsuha to you--
-Shut up.
-Hmm.
It seems you underestimate me.
I have no need for the
protection of a half-demon.
Hmm!
-See that?
The power of sheer will.
-I guess you want some more.
Gah!
-Sesshomaru!
-How's that feel?
You will now suffer the
wrath of Lord Sesshomaru,
a mighty demon.
Take Kagome.
-I've got her.
-Oh no!
We forgot Master Jaken!
-Don't worry.
He should be fine.
-Huh?
-He's following us!
-He's after Kohaku's
Jewel shard.
-Yah!
-[giggling] Go on.
Tear me to pieces.
I'm just borrowing this body.
-Who are you, anyway?
-Since you ask, I'll tell you.
My name's Magatsuhi.
-You're Magatsuhi?
-Magatsuhi?
-The evil will within
the Shikon Jewel.
-Hmm.
It must have found a way
to manifest as a demon.
-Ha.
I don't care if
you are Magatsuhi.
I'll still cut you down!
-All right.
But I'll take the dog with me.
-(THINKING) Lord Sesshomaru
can't even break free when
he's using his true
power as a dog demon.
Although, while
he's in that form,
he can only rely
on brute strength.
He is a dog, after all.
And from the look of
it, not a bright one.
If he undid the
transformation, he'd
shrink, and be
able to slip free.
But right now, that
won't occur to him.
Oh Lord Sesshomaru!
That's Lord Sesshomaru for ya.
No, I wasn't thinking anything.
I swear.
-That means Master Jaken
was thinking something.
-Yes.
It seems the two of them
are connected somehow.
-All right, Sesshomaru.
Leave him to me.
-Yah!
I know you don't want my help.
But I can't let you die.
Now watch out.
I'll use Meido Zangetsuha.
-[chuckling]
-What?
-By all means, give that
Meido Zangetsuha a whirl.
But be careful where you aim.
You could just as easily
end up killing your friends.
-Follow me.
-Huh?
-Whatever could he be doing?
-Isn't it obvious?
He's gathering Magatsuhi's
body parts in one place.
-I see.
This way the Meido
won't touch us.
-[giggling] How clever.
Now you won't end up
hurting your friends.
Still, how long do
you think you'll last?
-Sesshomaru would actually
risk his life for InuYasha
and the rest of us?
-I'm not surprised.
Lord Sesshomaru's a good person
once you get to know him.
-OK, you'll have to
defend yourselves now.
-Huh?
-Sesshomaru!
-Magatsuhi, he must
die by my hand.
My very pride is at stake.
[metal clanging]
[metal resonating]
-Huh?
[resonating continues]
-Whoa, well that was faster
than I expected, Sesshomaru.
Well, here we go again.
Go!
-[giggling]
-(THINKING) I could smell it,
the true form of Magatsuhi
that's manipulating
these other parts.
The scent is slightly different
from Naraku's rotten stench.
-Sesshomaru, you idiot.
Come back!
-[gasp]
-Tenseiga?
-Will it work?
-Why use Tenseiga,
a sword that heals?
-Yeah, I thought that sword
couldn't cut anything.
-Because there is one
thing Tenseiga can cut.
-No!
Damn you!
-What is that?
-Perhaps it's
Magatsuhi's true form.
-I see.
Magatsuhi was formed
from the souls
of demons sealed
within the Jewel.
It seems Tenseiga's blade
is still effective, as long
as what it's cutting
is not of this world.
-You'll pay!
-Ha, how pathetic.
That sword may be able
to cut through souls.
But it will never be able to
cut through Naraku's flesh.
-Ah.
-[gasp]
-Sesshomaru!
-Now I'll say it one last time.
You are weak.
-Somebody help him!
-Damn it!
Sesshomaru, I don't care
if you don't want my help.
I won't leave you here to die.
-InuYasha.
-Oh no.
He's dead!
-Don't cry!
We should be celebrating
Lord Sesshomaru's courage.
He knew he'd lose, but
he chose to fight anyway.
-Master Jaken.
-Our tears would only
dishonor his magnificent end.
[weeping]
-(THINKING) Are you so proud
that you'd rather die than
accept help from the person who
took Meido Zangetsuha from you?
You idiot.
I won't accept that, Sesshomaru.
-[chuckling]
-Huh?
[grunting]
-What's wrong?
Why not use that
splendid sword of yours
to blow them all to pieces?
Oh, you needn't worry about
what will happen to him.
Even if he shattered
into little pieces,
he'll be restored-- as a part
of Naraku's body, that is.
-I'm going to get you for this!
Huh?
-Whoa!
-Sesshomaru?
-He's still alive?
-This sensation.
-Lord Sesshomaru.
-I'm so glad you're safe.
-Wha--
-Is that?
-Master Totosai.
-(THINKING) Totosai.
In that case, this is it.
-But how?
-Master Jaken, do you see that?
-I do.
-His arm.
-I-i-i-it's the arm
that InuYasha cut off.
-So it's finally
appeared, Sesshomaru.
Finally, a weapon that did
not belong to your father.
This is your sword, Bakusaiga.
-This is my new sword, is it?
Bakusaiga.
-Are they going
to combine again?
-What?
Not only can't I
regenerate, but now
even body parts that were
unscathed are coming apart.
-The effect of his
blade remains even now.
-Not only does it remain,
it continues to spread.
-(THINKING) If Naraku absorbs
any demons touched by that
sword, of the damage
will spread to him too.
-I'll admit this diversion has
proven to be very surprising.
However, as I am only
borrowing this body,
you've done me no harm.
Ah!
-Serves you right,
insolent talking head.
That's what you
get for attempting
to belittle Lord Sesshomaru!
-Where's Magatsuhi's true form?
-(THINKING) It escaped.
-How is she?
-She still hasn't woken up.
-Hmm.
-Lord Sesshomaru, I thought
you were going to die.
-I never once stopped
believing in your victory, Lord
Sesshomaru.
-(MIMICKING MOCKINGLY) Our
tears would only dishonor his
magnificent end.
-[gasp] Staff of two heads.
-Whoa!
That's hot.
Hot.
-Please show me your
Bakusaiga, Sesshomaru.
Hmm?
Hmm.
This sword has always been
a part of you, Sesshomaru.
It was waiting for you.
But before you
could wield it, you
needed to show you were worthy
of it by standing on your own
as a great demon.
-What's this?
Why, I'll have you know
Lord Sesshomaru has always
stood on his own.
-Will you shut up?
-Shutting up, sir.
-(THINKING) It
makes perfect sense.
Overcoming his
attachment to Tessaiga,
that was the test
for Sesshomaru.
He had to let go of the past.
TOTOSAI: You once lost
your left arm in an attempt
to take Tessaiga.
It was a most unfortunate event.
But now you have gained a new
arm, along with Bakusaiga,
a sword that is truly
yours, and yours alone,
proving that you have finally
surpassed your father,
and that you would have been
released from your obsession
with Tessaiga.
-[whimpering]
-Kagome, are you OK, Kagome?
-Yeah.
[music playing]
KAGOME: It's finally here,
entrance exams for high school.
I've been studying
for the past 10 days,
so I'm sure it will be fine.
I can definitely pass.
-We're going back, Kagome.
-Uh, uh!
Sit, boy!
What a nightmare.
I mean, why would you come
for me today of all days?
Next time on InuYasha the
Final Act, the day of days.
KAGOME: At this
point, I still didn't
realize that I
would one day have
to choose between two
worlds-- this one or his.