-Don't you have
someplace else to go?
Scram!
Be on your way!
-Watch it, Jaken!
Remember, we're only
here because you squirts
couldn't fend for yourselves!
-Who are you calling a squirt?
-Dah!
-Here, I'll make you taller!
-Stop this at once, you animal!
-Inuyasha, why do you always
have to be such a bully?
-Hey!
You're getting pretty
stretchy there, Jaken!
KAGOME: Cut it out, Inuyasha!
Sit, boy!
-I can't feel my legs!
[gasps]
-Lord Sesshomaru!
-Sesshomaru!
-Shouldn't you be getting
back, Lord Sesshomaru?
Ooh, impressive!
Trying to kill me
just like that.
Now please, hear me out.
I have something for
you, Lord Sesshomaru.
-Oh?
And what is that?
-I understand you're having
some trouble with your sword.
Don't glare at me, I know
everything that happened.
I even know that
Tenseiga was originally
a part of Inuyasha's Tessaiga.
-Humph, that may be true.
But what business
is it of yours?
-Draw Inuyasha.
-Huh?
-True Heir
-What you hold is a fragment
of Kanna's mirror demon.
If you shatter the
fragment, and spread it
over Tenseiga's
blade, you will be
able to capture
Tessaiga's abilities,
and make them your own.
-Hmm, this must
be Naraku's idea.
He wishes to pit me
against Inuyasha,
in the hope that we will
eliminate each other.
There's no other reason for him
to help me-- an obvious trap.
However, it is a
trap worth springing.
-Sesshomaru, what's going on?
Have you lost your mind?
-Silence!
I said draw!
-Ha!
Idiot!
You're still hung up about
Tessaiga, aren't you?
-Aaah!
-Ugh!
-All right, if that's
how it's going to be,
then I won't hold
back either, bastard!
Take this!
Wind Scar!
What?
[gasps]
-Wind Scar isn't working!
-The scent from
Tenseiga's blade.
It couldn't be.
-Wind Scar!
-What's going on Sesshomaru?
All right, why can I smell
Naraku's scent on your sword?
BYAKUYA: Actually,
that would be my scent.
-Byakuya!
The one and only.
I passed a fragment of
Kanna's mirror demon
on to Lord Sesshomaru.
I hope you don't mind.
-That's how Tenseiga was able
to steal Tessaiga's energy
and abilities.
-But Lord Sesshomaru, why?
While you were gone, Naraku
tried to kill Kohaku!
-He's evil!
You can't trust him!
Don't listen to what he says!
-Shhh!
Everyone's got an opinion, hm?
Let's go to a place where you
can fight without interruption.
-Wow!
-Is that the moon?
[gasps]
-It's disappearing!
-Oh no!
Where is he sending Inuyasha?
-Good question.
-Damn you!
-[inaudible] He got away!
-Ohh.
-It makes no sense.
I can't believe
that Lord Sesshomaru
would borrow Naraku's power.
-This is good.
There's no one around
to interrupt our battle.
-You disappoint me, Sesshomaru.
I never imagined
you'd sink this low!
-Adamant barrage!
You disappoint
me, too, Inuyasha.
Is this really the
extent of your abilities?
If so, it only
proves that you never
deserved to wield Tessaiga
in the first place.
Hmm, it would seem the
Scabbards barrier protected you.
-Sesshomaru!
You-- you were actually
trying to kill me!
-Yaa!
Yaa!
-If you prove yourself
weak, I'll kill you.
Then I'll get rid of Tessaiga
and Tenseiga for good!
Prove it, Inuyasha.
Prove that it is you who is
the rightful heir to Tessaiga.
That is all I ask.
-Prove it?
Humph!
So you're telling me if I
win, you'll let this go?
-Something like that.
BYAKUYA: Sesshomaru's
a mean one, indeed.
He shows no mercy.
It's clear he truly
hates Inuyasha--
NARAKU: And we shall
exploit that hatred.
Sesshomaru always believed that
Tessaiga should have been his.
He's never forgiven
Inuyasha for inheriting it.
-I see.
-So all we had to do is
give him a reason to attack.
And he took it, despite knowing
full well that it's a trap.
Sesshomaru will not
hesitate to kill Inuyasha.
He will destroy him
just as I desire.
-Yes.
In fact, he just
sent him flying.
-I sure hope Inuyasha's OK.
-Lord Sesshomaru.
-The sky sure is
getting dark, huh?
-Aaah!
-Mr. Totosai!
-Well now, it appears
they've already begun.
-Can you see them?
What's happening?
-Uh, you want to see?
-Yes, if you don't mind.
Hmm, OK.
[loud roar]
-Aaaah!
Yaa!
-Heh, you've turned into a
demon out of desperation?
[growl]
-Inuyasha!
-Look at his face.
-Yes, his demon blood must
have taken over to protect him.
-Tessaiga is seeking
my demonic energy.
-It's resonating with
Inuyasha's sword.
-The demonic energy
Tessaiga should have lost
is flowing into me, instead.
Sesshomaru!
The energy he stole
is flowing into me!
-Eeah!
-Yaa!
I can do this!
-Heh, just crossing
blades with him
caused all of the
demonic energy to escape.
NARAKU: You really want to
return to Inuyasha, don't you?
-Wind Scar!
-Humph!
Backlash Wave!
-Is that all you've got?
Come on, Tessaiga!
-Backlash Wave!
-He countered with the
exact same technique!
-This time, I'm going to
take back adamant barrage!
Ugh!
Dah!
-Meido Zangetsuha!
-Yaa!
-Augh!
Oh!
BYAKUYA: Oh my, would
you look at that!
Sesshomaru just hit him directly
with a Meido Tsangetsuha.
There's no running
away from that.
-Byakuya, I want
to see it myself.
-Eww, this is disgusting.
You can see with that thing?
-Yes-- and clearly.
Inuyasha hurtling down the
path to the underworld.
-Meido Tsangetsuha
is a technique
I developed and trained for.
If you are truly
fated to inherit it,
show me then, and
take it from me.
Right here.
Right now.
-Damn it!
I can't do a thing!
Isn't there anything?
There must be!
What should we do now?
Tessaiga?
-Is that all it took, Inuyasha?
And to think you
were supposed to be
the true heir to Tessaiga.
Father, this is the end.
Farewell!
Be gone to the underworld--
along with Inuyasha!
Hm?
-Huh?
Tessaiga!
This is Dragon-scaled Tessaiga.
What is this happening?
Am I supposed to cut
through some demonic energy?
But where is it?
The only demonic energy
out here is my own.
What am I supposed to cut with
this Dragon-scaled Tessaiga?
-That's Inuyasha's
demonic energy.
-I wonder-- will he be able to
understand Tessaiga's desire?
-Huh?
-It's desire?
-Inuyasha won't to be able
to escape this predicament,
unless he comes to
understand Tessaiga's will.
-He can do it!
Inuyasha and that sword have
fought together a long time!
It's only a matter of time
before he figures it out.
-OK, but even if he
does figure it out,
will he be able to execute it?
-He'll be fine!
-Yes!
Inuyasha can do it.
-Yeah, I agree.
-Maybe, but Inuyasha is
stupid and thick-headed.
-And he's got a mean streak!
BYAKUYA: This
Dragon-scaled Tessaiga--
it cuts the foe's demon
vortex-- the source
of their demonic energy, right?
-Yes, but the path to the
underworld's no demon.
He cannot cut through it, for it
has no demonic energy or demon
vortex.
-Huh?
My demon vortex!
Am I supposed to cut through it?
-I'm sure you realize that to
cut through your demon vortex
would mean taking your own life.
So Inuyasha, are you
capable of doing that?
-Hm!
Grrr!
Come on, Tessaiga!
I believe in you.
I'll do this!
Ah!
Augh!
I can feel it!
The demonic energy is flowing
through me and Tessaiga!
-This is it.
This is proof that Inuyasha is
the rightful heir to the sword.
[gasps]
-That was faster
than I expected.
-Huh?
-Tessaiga and
Tenseiga-- Can't you
see the two swords are
attempting to join as one?
-His demonic energy is
eating into the path
to the underworld.
BYAKUYA: What are
you going to do?
It would seem this trap has
only made Inuyasha stronger.
-(CHUCKLING) Clearly,
I have no choice,
but to end his life myself.
And I'll do it using the sword
that Sesshomaru abandoned.
-OK.
Good, Tessaiga.
Keep this up, and soon
we'll be free of the path
of the underworld!
-Augh!
That's Sesshomaru's sword!
NARAKU: (LAUGHING) The fragment
of Kanna's mirror demon
that I gave to Sesshomaru,
is still on this sword!
-Naraku!
NARAKU: That's right.
This sword is a part of me, just
as Kanna's mirror demon was.
I can control it effortlessly!
-Miasma.
-Naraku!
Ya!
Yaa!
-Augh!
-Naraku!
Ugh!
What the--?
Sesshomaru.
NARAKU: Ha ha!
Now that Inuyasha has weakened,
he's here to reclaim his sword.
As you wish, Sesshomaru.
I shall let you finish
him off yourself.
-Naraku, I already
know what must be done.
Raise your sword, Inuyasha.
-Ha!
As if you had to ask!
-Aaah!
-This fight is between
myself and Inuyasha.
Naraku, you no longer have
a part to play in this.
-The fragments are coming off!
Huh?
Tenseiga!
A black blade-- what is this?
-Meido Tsangetsuha.
-They have become one.
Poof!
-I know it doesn't
make any sense,
but it almost looked
as though Sesshomaru
broke Tenseiga on purpose.
-Fools!
Now they have lost
their means to exit
the path to the underworld.
-Damn!
Naraku's miasma.
Ugh!
-It's over!
Now that Inuyasha's
demonic energy is gone,
you're both destined
to spend eternity
on the path to the underworld.
-Succumbing to Naraku's poison,
your nature is weak half-demon.
-Ugh!
-Hey!
How will they escape from
the path of the underworld?
-There's no way!
I'm afraid it's impossible now!
-What?
-Oh no!
Sesshomaru-- What?
Do you still want to fight?
-Their path has been closed.
-What?
-Will we stay here on the
path to the underworld?
Or will we find
some way to return
to the world of the living?
Inuyasha, it all depends on you.
-It depends on me?
But how?
Are you telling me I need
to use this new Tessaiga?
This black Tessaiga?
-We don't have any time
to waste on conversation.
-Huh!
My body!
What do I do?
Where am I supposed to cut?
-Inuyasha, that sword
belongs to you now.
You must wield it your own way.
[gasp]
-Don't you disappear on me!
I won't be able to live
with myself if you die now.
It's bad enough
I've got your sword!
-Yaaaa!
Light!
Ugh!
Over there!
Augh!
Let's go!
-The path!
-Whoa!
Is that--?
-Inuyasha!
-Sesshomaru!
-You're hurt.
-Sesshomaru, are you able
to accept what has happened?
-Lord Sesshomaru, I am
literally sick with grief!
For Tenseiga to be
absorbed into Tessaiga
like that-- it's unbearable!
-I do not care.
We're leaving, Jaken.
-One moment, Sesshomaru.
Although you may find little
consolation in it now,
I suggest you take it.
It fell from the path
to the underworld.
-You OK, Inuyasha?
[gasp]
-That's-- that's Tenseiga.
-Wasn't that sword
broken already?
I see, that light
I was following
must have come from Tenseiga.
-You may not be satisfied with
this sword that cannot cut.
But Tenseiga is
powerful, for it heals.
-So what?
I'm supposed to take it and
go around healing people now?
Don't be ridiculous.
-Aaah!
Please wait, Lord Sesshomaru!
-Um--
-Huh?
-I'll give it to him when
he's in a better mood.
I promise!
-Goodbye.
Take care, sister!
-Kohaku!
-I guess he's made up his mind.
-Hey, Totosai.
-Hmm?
-What's going to
happen to Sesshomaru?
Everything our father
gave us is now mine.
There's nothing left.
-If I were you, I'd be
worrying less about my brother,
and more about mastering
a new Tessaiga!
-Yeah!
-You do realize you
had help, right?
You didn't escape from the path
to the underworld on your own.
-Yeah.
If I hadn't been guided
by Tenseiga's light,
I never would have made it back.
-Besides, Sesshomaru
hasn't realized this yet,
but he's one step away from
obtaining a weapon of his own.
And he'll be pleased to
learn that this one is not
an heirloom from his father.
[theme music]
-Kagome has been trapped
by a dead priestess, who's
under Naraku's control.
-Choose, Kagome.
Will you allow
Hitomiko to kill you?
Or will you shoot the spider
nesting within her to escape?
-If I use my bow
and fight, I won't
be able to save Lady Hitomiko!
What should I do?
-Next time, on
Inuyasha-- The Final Act.
Hitomiko's Burial.
-You are no more than
a bird in a cage.
You shall never leave-- never!