[music playing]
[theme music]
-Miroku and Sango are taking
way too long to come back.
I guess they must
be having trouble
with that bone-collecting demon.
-Why does this have to
happen now of all times?
-It's the new moon.
There's nothing we
can do about it.
-I never should have let the two
of them go there by themselves.
-I can see it.
Right over there.
-You mustn't breathe
that in, Sango.
It's a cloud of poison.
-Miroku, just
promise me you won't
use your wind tunnel on it.
Hiraikotsu!
What?
-Thank you.
This is an exquisite bone.
-It's trying to eat Hiraikotsu.
-Stand back, Sango.
-Miroku, no!
-Wind Tunnel!
Got it.
-Thank you, Miroku.
Hiraikotsu.
MIROKU (VOICEOVER):
This scar hurts.
How pathetic.
I can't even endure the
poison of a weak demon.
-I've been searching for quite
some time for a bone that
might help my father
recover from his ailments.
And thanks to you, at
last, I've found it.
-I knew at first
taste Hiraikotsu
was formed from the bones of
many different demons, which
is why it will make the
perfect medicine for me.
-You cannot have it.
-Go on.
Throw it at me again.
-Sango, we should pull back now.
-It's useless.
There's nowhere for you to run.
INUYASHA: "Sango's Feelings.
Miroku's Resolve."
-Smashing Top!
-Inuyasha, we should hurry.
-Dammit.
Is the new moon still out?
--[laughing] I shall consume you
both, along with Hiraikotsu.
-We're going to break
out of here, Sango.
You can't.
It's too dangerous.
[grunt]
-Damn you.
Trying to swallow
me from the inside.
MIROKU: Poison.
-Don't.
That's enough.
Are you OK?
-Didn't I try to warn you?
You're wasting your time.
Resistance is pointless.
There's nowhere for you to run.
-I shall start by eating the
bones of the troublesome monk.
-Very well then, you
may have Hiraikotsu.
However, I want your word that
no harm will come to the monk.
Promise me that, and
the bone is yours.
-How absurd.
Obviously, you still
don't understand
the situation you're in.
I will get what I want
whether you obey or resist.
You are in no
position to negotiate.
[demonic laughter]
Both of you will
die, and Hiraikotsu
will belong to father.
It's that simple.
-I understand.
Now, I know what
needs to be done.
This demon-slaying
salve is strong enough
to dissolve Hiraikotsu.
Try eating Hiraikotsu now.
Take this.
-[gasp] Father, no.
Miroku, are you OK?
-Damn you, woman.
How dare you do that
to beloved father?
-Adamant Barrage!
[scream]
-Hey, Sango, Miroku, are you OK?
-Sango.
-It's OK, Miroku.
It's over.
Forgive me, Hiraikotsu.
-Sango?
-I knew what would happen
when I applied the poison.
It was inevitable.
-Forgive me, Sango.
If only I'd been
strong enough to fight.
-What are you talking, Miroku?
You risked your life when
you used your Wind Tunnel
to help me.
So don't apologize.
-So what'll you do now?
-This is a disaster.
How are you supposed to
fight without Hiraikotsu?
-Come on, Shippo.
Don't give up so easily.
I mean there's got to be
a way to fix it, right?
Why of course, there is.
-Huh?
SHIPPO: Myoga.
-Now, master, as
your loyal servant,
I shall gladly introduce you to
one who could fix Hiraikotsu.
KAGOME: The Master of Potions?
MYOGA: As the name
suggests, he's
a demon sage who administers
herbal remedies and poisons.
-And you think this
Master of Potions
can remove the poison
from Hiraikotsu.
-Oh, he can.
He's more than capable,
but whether or not
he will depends on
how much he likes you.
-It's incredible.
-Hey, Myoga.
You want to tell me why this
waterfall reeks like alcohol?
-That's because it is alcohol.
[collective gasp]
-Look at that.
SHIPPO: What's with
all those jugs?
-Master Inuyasha, you must bring
one of those jugs over here.
Very good.
Now dump it out.
-Like this?
-Now then, if you
please, barkeep.
-Who is this guy?
-The Master of Potions.
-He just looks like a
drunken old man to me.
-Hey, wake up.
MASTER OF POTIONS: You expect
me to remove the poison
from your weapon?
INUYASHA: Yes.
We've heard that you would
be able to do so, Master.
MASTER OF POTIONS:
Let me have a look.
-So you can fix it?
-Demon-slaying salve.
That's some harsh
stuff you put on it.
Even if I could fix it, I'd
refuse to do it on principle.
-At a glance, I can tell you
this weapon is well-worn.
This suggests
you've been fighting
with it for a long time.
Yet you'd apply this vicious
poison to it without a thought.
That doesn't sit well with me.
-Look.
You don't even know the
whole story behind it.
[vomiting]
That was gross.
-I forget to mention, I'm
a little bit hung over.
SANGO: That's enough, Inuyasha.
The Master of Potions
is right after all.
There's no excuse
for what I did.
-What?
So you're just going
to give up now?
-Fine.
I'll do it.
-Huh?
A second ago you said
you wouldn't do it.
-That's because I thought
it belonged to you.
But your friend
here, I like her.
-Apparently, the
Master of Potions
has a soft spot for girls.
-Well, obviously, he's
a good person at heart.
-If by good person, you
mean pervert, then yes.
-Young lady, let's have
a look at your hand.
Hm.
-What are you doing?
-You misunderstand.
-Perhaps, he's a little
too good of a person.
-I was merely examining the
strength in her legs and waist.
You see, though I agreed
to fix your weapon.
In reality, you are the one
who must fight and risk death.
-Risk death?
-Correct.
Now, be kind and hand
over Hiraikotsu, dear.
-Hey, the whole
thing's dissolving.
-Poison will do that.
-Poison?
But I though you
were going to fix it.
-Hiraikotsu will be fixed
when this poison turns
into a remedy.
-OK.
So now what happens?
-Well, mainly, I need you to
slay the demons inside this jug
here.
The poison in Hiraikotsu's
jug will turn into a remedy
if you can pacify
the demons within it.
Put another way, if you aren't
able to pacify the demons,
Hiraikotsu will
dissolve into nothing.
Do you follow me?
-Understood.
I'll do it.
-Sango.
-You can't.
-Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
-Hey, is it really OK to
trust this drunken sage?
I mean he seems a bit insane.
-It's a bit late for that now.
-It doesn't matter
what's in there.
I'll do whatever it takes
to bring Hiraikotsu back.
SANGO (VOICEOVER):
That's strange.
I can breathe.
I just need to slay
all these demons.
Hold on, Hiraikotsu.
I promise I'll save you.
Their skin's too hard.
My sword's useless.
-I can't see a thing.
-I sure hope Sango's OK.
-Hey, hey, is this your idea
of fun, staring into a jug?
I don't know about
you, but I'm bored.
Why not raise a glass with me?
It's no fun to drink alone.
-Shut up, you old drunkard.
-Now, now, don't
get so worked up.
Upsy daisy.
This is alcohol.
-Of course, it is.
[hiccuping and laughing]
-Oh come on, Myoga.
Not you too.
-Look here.
I'm not drunk.
I'll have you know, I'm
watching over, Sango.
-You can see Sango
if you drink that?
-Absolutely positively.
-(DRUNKENLY) He's right.
I can see her.
-Of course.
-Maybe you're just
hallucinating.
-No, that liquid is the
Master of Potion's magic brew.
It enables whoever drinks
it to see inside the jug
that Sango entered.
Well, Inuyasha, is
Sango all right?
-Sure.
Although, it looks [hiccup]
like she's having a rough time.
-Why don't you
come out of there?
SANGO (VOICEOVER): It's strange.
Their eyes are filled
with such rage,
and yet it seems they
don't intend to kill me.
What's going on?
What do they want?
-Master of Potions, how
much longer until Hiraikotsu
dissolves completely?
-How much longer, huh?
Well, that's hard to say.
Are you planning to
jump in and help her?
It's useless.
I assure you.
You won't be able to reach her.
-I am not drunk.
-You are more than drunk.
-I ain't drunk, Kagome.
Can you tell me
one thing though?
Why are there two of you?
What do you think
you're doing, huh?
-See?
You go in one, and
you come out another.
Besides, monk, you've
got bigger fish to fry.
Isn't that right?
-What?
-Oh, what are you doing?
-I was just about
to ask you that.
-Your body is being consumed
by poison, is it not?
And a vicious poison to boot.
-Who are your two friends?
Aren't you going
to introduce us?
-OK.
OK.
-Over here.
-I can't breathe.
You don't want the
others to hear.
Is that it?
MIROKU: Please
keep this a secret.
-Very well.
Show me your right arm.
-Was it that obvious to you?
-Oh, that can only
come from miasma.
-It inches toward my heart
every time I use my Wind Tunnel.
It's spread more quickly
than I'd expected.
-I can only imagine
that sucking in poison
must be very
painful for you now.
-Indeed.
My tolerance for poison
is not what it was.
-Hm.
I've got something that
could help with that.
The way I see it, even if
Hiraikotsu were to be repaired,
Sango wouldn't think twice
about sacrificing it again
if it meant saving
your life, good monk.
DEMON: Why?
-Huh?
-Why did you apply poison to us?
SANGO (VOICEOVER): These voices?
MASTER OF POTIONS:
It would appear
that Hiraikotsu was created
from the bones of many demons.
-I'm amazed you could tell.
-I can see many
things, young man.
SANGO (VOICEOVER): It's you.
You're Hiraikotsu.
-Sango must answer to the
souls of all those demons
that were used to create
Hiraikotsu in the first place.
MIROKU: But if those demons
are part of Hiraikotsu,
why did you tell
her to slay them?
-I suppose I meant
it figuratively,
but I also told
her to pacify them.
-So you're saying, she
needs their forgiveness.
-Anyway, let's get
back to your issue.
Shall we?
MASTER OF POTIONS:
This is the medicine.
At the same time, it is
also a strong poison.
SANGO (VOICEOVER): Hiraikotsu.
DEMON: We have fought by your
side from the very beginning.
We believed that through
countless battles
a bond was forged between us,
one that could not be broken.
And now you have poisoned us.
You have betrayed us.
SANGO (VOICEOVER): Hiraikotsu.
-If you drink this and
manage to survive it,
you will be freed
from all pain when
you suck in miasma or
poison in the future,
that much I can guarantee you.
-No more pain.
You mean I'll no longer
feel what's happening.
-I wonder what those two
are discussing over there.
Inuyasha?
-Stay here.
-That is correct.
Whatever happens to
you will still happen.
You just won't feel it.
But those wounds from
the miasma won't heel.
On the contrary, they'll--
-I'll drink it.
-You need to hear what
I'm going to say first.
-Yes, I already know
what you're going to say.
-Huh.
It's poison.
-Yes, it certainly
is poison, one
that will allow you to
fight without feeling
any of the pain.
However, it won't stop
the damage from the miasma
from spreading.
Eventually, pain or no pain,
it will spread to your heart,
and you will die.
-You crazy old drunk.
How dare you offer
him this crap?
MIROKU: Stop, Inuyasha.
Look, I understand
the implications,
but you must understand
it's getting worse.
-I know that.
You think I didn't notice.
The scent of miasma
from your body's
been growing stronger every day.
-Exactly.
-What do you think will happen
to Sango if you die, huh?
-Why do you not resist us?
-Didn't the Master of
Potions tell you to slay us.
-Yes.
Didn't he tell you to slay us?
SANGO (VOICEOVER): There's
no way I can do that.
I refuse.
Hiraikotsu, if you
will accept me,
I wish to fight by
your side again.
-Then swear it will
not happen again.
Swear that you will
never betray us again.
Swear to us now
that next time you
will abandon the human man
instead of sacrificing us.
Only then, shall we return
to you as Hiraikotsu.
-Forgive me, Hiraikotsu.
I cannot make that promise.
-Why not?
-Because I won't be
able to live if he dies.
-Hm.
If you're willing to
sacrifice your life
for the sake of a human man,
then we shall take it now.
INUYASHA: Don't you get it?
If you drink this
medicine, you won't
hesitate to use the Wind Tunnel.
In other words,
you're just going
to end up killing
yourself sooner.
-Inuyasha, are you
telling me not to fight?
I should allow myself
to be protected instead.
If I can't use the
Wind Tunnel, Sango
will only push herself
harder to compensate for me.
-You just can't stand being
protected by a woman, huh?
-That's right.
If it means her life
is in danger, I can't.
Sango would risk her
life to protect me,
but I won't let her do it.
-Your stupid pride's
going to kill you.
-Listen to me.
You seem convinced that
I'm rushing to my death.
But my decision has
nothing to do with that.
Don't you see it.
Drinking this medicine
will determine how I live.
I want to fight,
so I can survive.
So I can protect her.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): Miroku?
-What's wrong?
Aren't you going
to argue with him?
-Shut up.
I could never beat this
guy in an argument.
-Inuyasha, this
goes without saying,
but please do not tell
Sango or Kagome about this.
-I won't tell them, but you
have to promise me something,
that you won't use your
Wind Tunnel unless it's
a matter of life and death.
Sango might forgive you for
killing yourself, but I won't.
-We have a deal.
Thank you, friend.
-Sango, this is
your last chance.
Swear.
Swear that you will
never betray us again.
SANGO (VOICEOVER):
I can't do that.
-Even though we
will tear you apart.
-Hiraikotsu, I refuse to make
a promise that I cannot keep.
-You're willing to
sacrifice yourself.
Does this monk really
mean that much to you?
-He does.
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): It hurts.
It's as if my body
is burning up inside.
-Hey, is this normal?
-Hey, is everything OK?
-This is bad.
We're nowhere near finished.
Oh, I know.
[scream]
It was the only way to
keep that girl away.
I swear.
-Right.
-I can't have anyone
disturbing him
until he's adapted
to the poison.
Now, go keep her busy,
and let me handle this.
Shh.
-Inuyasha, what's
wrong with him?
-Turns out Miroku's
a lightweight.
Go figure.
-I see.
That's what happened.
-Hurts, doesn't it?
Do you regret your decision?
-No regrets.
I just have to endure this
a little while longer.
Then no more pain.
-Sango, even now, the monk
is being consumed by miasma.
He is nothing more
than a burden upon you.
-Yes, I know that, but the monk
has risked his life many times
to save me.
-And for that, you're
willing to throw away
your own life to
save a dying man?
-I have no intention of
throwing my life away.
-What?
-I plan to survive and
share my life with the monk.
Knowing that he's
alive is what gives me
the courage to live on.
Hiraikotsu, I beg of you.
Please lend both of
us your strength.
MIROKU (VOICEOVER): Sango.
Sango.
SANGO (VOICEOVER): Hiraikotsu.
-Oh.
-Look at that.
The water's starting
to clear up.
-Does that mean the poison's
turned into a remedy?
-We are demons, Sango.
We cannot understand your
human affection and empathy.
However, we have just
felt the monk's resolve,
and that we do understand.
-We have decided we shall
support you once more.
DEMON: We shall fight
by your side again.
SANGO (VOICEOVER):
Oh, Hiraikotsu.
Thank you.
-What you probably
didn't realize
was that all of my herbs and
poisons are interconnected.
You see the poison which
entered your body has changed
the poison in the
jug into a remedy.
Now then, how do you feel?
-I feel much better.
It's unbelievable.
-It would seem that everything
worked out for this one
as well.
-Miroku.
-Sango.
INUYASHA (VOICEOVER): Miroku.
-Just so we're clear.
The monk's body
hasn't recovered.
You understand that, right?
He merely can't feel the
pain from his wounds anymore.
The damage from
the miasma remains.
-I know.
And I'm grateful even for that.
SANGO: Master of
Potions, you've helped
restore Hiraikotsu
to the way it was.
I can't thank you enough.
-The way it was.
You forget that your Hiraikotsu
has been swimming around
in my herbs and poisons.
It will never be the
way it was as you say.
However, it won't be evident
to you until you fight again.
When you do, don't be surprised
by how it may have changed.
[theme music]
-I'll have you know Meido
Zangetsuha was originally
my technique.
One practitioner is
all that's needed,
especially considering
Tenseiga's an incomplete blade.
To the underworld with you.
KOHAKU: Lord
Sesshomaru's Meido has
been absorbed by
Shishinki's Meido.
INUYASHA: Sesshomaru
draw Tenseiga.
I think something might happen.
Next time on InuYasha The
Final Act, "A Complete Meido."
SESSHOMARU: Tenseiga?
Are you telling me to fight
together with Tessaiga?