Why aren't
you in bed...?
Having trouble sleeping?
[IZUMIKO] I can't
believe it...
It's awful...
and I don't know what
I'm supposed to do now!
I don't understand...
Did something happen?
[IZUMIKO] It's Sagara...
I...
I put him through
such a nightmare.
Even he was scared
by the end of it...
and why wouldn't he be...?
I'm the enemy of all mankind!
I'm serious...!
Before long...
I don't even think
I'll be myself anymore!
♪
[KISARAGI] The Executive
Committee's job is simple...
Patrol the festival, and offer
help to anyone who needs it...
If you run into
trouble, please inform
festival director Hayakawa.
Of course, you'll
need to refer to
your individual schedules...
From time to time,
I'm sure you'll want to see
how your class is doing.
But please remain neutral when
checking the popularity polls...
That should be it.
[ALL] Yes ma'am!
Thanks!
Enjoy the festival!
We're going to outsell
everybody today!
I can just feel it!
Hey, Suzuhara...!
Is it strange not
wearing your pigtails?
My hair's
still in braids.
They're just
wrapped up in buns...
Mayura gave me a hand with it.
[MANATSU] Really...?
I wanna see...!
Lemme look!
[IZUMIKO] I can't...
The style's not appropriate
for the festival.
[IZUMIKO gasps]
[IZUMIKO screams]
[TAKASE] Just look at you...!
That is adorable!
Can I have that
back now, please?
That is just the cutest thing
in the world!
Seriously,
you look great!
Yeah...!
I wish my hair
would do that!
You're like a
little China doll!
I only did it like
this because I have to
wear the hat.
Who says?
Remember, our class's theme
is "Rebelling Against Tyranny."
Which means we can
do anything we want!
[TAKASE] Class 1-A's theme is
the Tenshou Boy Ambassadors--
after the boys who were
sent West in the 1500s.
This is called sponge cake...
Would you like a slice...?
It's nice and light.
And delicious, as well.
[TAKAYANAGI] May I offer
you a piece of sponge cake?
It's a special recipe
from Portugal.
One bite, and you will
be transported to--
Side with me.
The real battle will be
decided during the festival.
[IZUMIKO clears her throat]
Am I interrupting?
Of course not,
Suzuhara...!
Please, check out
our exhibition...
We're using the data that
we gathered in Togakushi.
[IZUMIKO]
"Popularity forecasts"?
[RYOUGOKU] Yes, exactly...!
Basically, we're gathering and
controlling information...
After all, that's what
the ninja did during
the Warring States Period.
[IZUMIKO] These "forecasts" look
an awful lot like gambling.
[RYOUGOKU] That's our secret...
Festival Director Hayakawa is
the one behind these forecasts.
[IZUMIKO] Is he, really?
[MIDDLE SCHOOL GIRL 1]
Hello...?
I'm sorry...
Are you Suzuhara?
[IZUMIKO] Oh...
uh...
Yes, that's me.
Thank goodness!
We really need your help.
None of us wants
to be the princess!
The princess?
Are you talking about
the middle school parade?
Why not?
Don't you know?
Anybody who dresses up as
the princess will be cursed!
[IZUMIKO] By any chance...
is this connected to why
the model dropped out
of the clothing demo?
Well yeah, but you were the one
who took her place, and nothing
out of the ordinary happened
to you after wearing
the costume, did it?
No, nothing out of
the ordinary, I suppose.
That's why we wanted to ask you
if you would please be the
princess in today's parade!
Huh?!
We've kept pictures of you from
the clothing demonstration as
good luck charms, but even so,
we're still really scared
of what might happen to us.
Hold on a minute!
I can't!
Don't you see what I'm wearing?
Excuse me.
What exactly do you
think you're doing?
The Executive Committee
has a meeting...
You can't just spirit her away.
But we're
scared, Sagara.
Your parade can get by
without a princess.
You don't need to push
Suzuhara into doing it...
and you should be ashamed
of yourselves for trying to.
[MIYUKI] Those younger girls
were taking advantage of you...
Doesn't that make you
feel a little pathetic?
They were scared...
[MIYUKI] Don't let people
walk all over you!
This coming from
the guy who did anything
the Hime-gami wanted him to.
That's unfair...!
Do you have any idea
how difficult it is to deal
with someone like her?
The whole time
she was in control,
I was fighting desperately
to get you back!
[WOMAN] Um, excuse me.
I'm so sorry, but do
you know of any place
where I could change a diaper?
[IZUMIKO] Oh, of course.
You're welcome to use
the Administrative Tower...
After you leave this building,
you just head to your left...
From there you should--
[IZUMIKO gasps]
That doesn't
belong to you, sweetie!
[WOMAN] No, no...!
You know better...
Give that back!
I'm very
sorry about that.
[IZUMIKO] No...
it's okay.
Hey!
Why are you laughing at me...?
What's so funny?
I'm sorry!
I think I'm just
a little hysterical...
The Hime-gami had me scared
pretty much out of my wits
the other night...
Then I see you with that hair...
[IZUMIKO] You weren't the only
one surprised by her appearance,
you know.
[MIYUKI] For your information,
when the Hime-gami shows up,
it isn't on a whim.
She only appears
whenever she wants
to prevent calamity
from occurring...
not because she wants to bring
it about, like I thought...
I see that now...
She only possesses you when
she has something dire to say.
It sounds like you
would rather spend time with
the Hime-gami than with me.
I never said that...!
If I wanted to keep you as the
Hime-gami do you really think
I would have gone with her
to the castle ruins and fought
to bring you back?
That's right.
You went out on a date
with her, didn't you...?
There was a little
spark there, huh?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you going off
on me like this?
Just forget it!
Mayura understands how I feel
a lot better than you do.
Whoa, hold on.
What do you mean by that...?
You didn't tell her about--
So you know...
I don't really appreciate
listening to you talk about
other girls.
[HIME-GAMI] Enough of this.
I do not like it when
you speak of other women
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara...
have you ever considered that
you and the Hime-gami might
have more in common
than you think...?
That you're the same?
What are you talking about?
It's prob'ly nothing...
Just forget it.
[KISARAGI] Having the parade
without the princess?
I suspect Hayakawa would
be less than pleased.
[REINA] Keep in mind our
foremost obligation is
to respect the
participants' wishes.
[KISARAGI] Yes,
you have a point...
Moving on.
Five people have gotten
sick in the Horror House...
and all five happened
just this morning.
They're recuperating
in the infirmary.
What is going on?
Did they make it
too frightening?
No.
We checked it
out earlier,
and it seems like they
kept it fairly tame.
[KISARAGI] I'm not sure I can
trust your opinion on that.
Yeah...?!
Then go check it
out for yourself.
You'll see--
No way in hell!
If you want...
I could go and
investigate.
Oh, really...?
I'd appreciate that,
thank you very much.
Damn Sagara...
Why couldn't I play the
role of the hero for once?
So the Prez is majorly
scared of ghosts, huh?
I'll talk to the middle
schoolers about the parade.
Maybe I can talk
some sense into them.
[KISARAGI] We've got the right
people on the right jobs...
Thanks, guys.
[MAYURA] The only people getting
sick in the Haunted House
are girls and women...?
Something doesn't seem
right about this...
There's that
"curse" thing, too...
[MIYUKI] Think it's Takayanagi?
[MAYURA] It's too soon to say.
Sagara!
Be sure to keep an
eye on Izumiko, okay?
Yeah...
Let's go.
I'll go.
You wait outside...
Okay?
What...?
Why?
We know something
strange is going on here...
There's no need to take risks...
I'll be back.
[BOY 1] Hey...
Suzuhara?
[BOY 1] Yeah,
I thought it was you...!
Do...
you mind if I take your
picture really quick...?
Like to remember you by?
[IZUMIKO] Huh...?
Um, I--
[BOY 2] Please?
It's not asking too much to let
my buddy get his photo with you.
[BOY 1] Nah man,
I don't actually need to be
in it with her.
I just want a shot of
her to send to my folks.
[BOY 1] You looked
great as the princess
at the demo.
But this has its own charm.
I have some work to
do for the Executive Committee.
I have to go!
[BOY 1]
Please, wait a sec!
Why did they
want my picture...?
I could understand
if it was Mayura.
[GIRL screams]
Scary!
Let's keep going.
[FEMALE GHOST 1]
It's you, Milady...
Oh, thank goodness...!
We couldn't find you.
[FEMALE GHOST 2]
We need to hurry...!
Please, Milady!
[FEMALE GHOST 3]
We haven't much time...!
The enemy will be
here any moment!
[FEMALE GHOST 4]
Quickly, please!
Come with us.
[FEMALE GHOST 5]
This is the way!
Leave me alone!
I don't want to go with you!
[FEMALE GHOST 1]
If only Ojtero were here...
[FEMALE GHOST 3] Then this
never would have come to pass.
What are you
talking about...?
Please let me go!
[FEMALE GHOSTS]
Please, Milady!
Hurry, Milady!
You must hurry!
Please, Milady!
Hurry, Milady!
You must hurry!
Sagara!
Milady, this way!
Milady!
[IZUMIKO] Is it really you?
Help, Sagara!
[MAN]
I've got you now.
[IZUMIKO screams]
[MIYUKI] What's
going on in here?
[IZUMIKO cries]
[MAN]
Uh, sorry, man.
[MIYUKI] Okay, what did you see
while you were in there...?
I'm not mad at you
for blowing me off...
Just tell me.
I'm pretty sure I had
my first ghost encounter.
And you didn't defend
yourself, did you...?
I taught you that
technique so you'd use it.
[IZUMIKO] I could tell they
went through something awful.
I felt bad.
Unbelievable...
May you be healed.
May the spiritual wounds
you've suffered be repaired.
What was that chant?
[MIYUKI] A Mudra, it'll
help you feel better...
I hope so, anyway.
Well, thank you...
I think I can feel it working.
[MIYUKI] Let's go
to the infirmary.
But why?
I'm really doing a lot better.
I didn't say we were
going there for you...
We have
investigating to do.
What the heck's
going on here?
[IZUMIKO] I think
I might know...
Please excuse me for a moment.
[MIYUKI] I should've known...
You really are a disgusting
specimen of humanity.
I'm volunteering.
Is that so bad?
[MIYUKI] Don't
give me that crap!
You've been crying,
haven't you...?
Why?
What happened?
Its nothing I uh
What?
Was it Miyuki's fault?
No, of course not...!
I was just a little
startled, that's all.
We were at the Horror House,
and I saw what I think
were ghosts, so...
In other words...
You encountered
something frightening,
and Miyuki was
no help whatsoever.
[IZUMIKO] No, you've
got it wrong...
It was my fault.
I didn't think
they meant me any harm...
Now I know I didn't
handle the situation well.
[YUKIMASA] Listen
to me carefully...
You must avoid blindly
sympathizing with ghosts...
I assure you, no good
will come out of it.
What do you mean?
[YUKIMASA] I mean, don't
go around feeling sorry
for dead people.
The Heavens look
upon the Earth...
Sympathy from above.
[IZUMIKO] What is this?
[YUKIMASA] We don't want
a halfwit protecting
the Hime-gami.
You think you can get
away with anything you want
so long as you say
it's necessary to
"protect the Hime-gami."
You really make me sick!
The wise man
makes use of every
opportunity he gets...
She will be highly guarded when
she enters the public eye...
You will only be allowed to
interact with Izumiko while
she is attending this academy.
What are you talking
about, Sagara...?
That totally contradicts
what you said the other day.
You told me the
Hime-gami chose Miyuki.
[YUKIMASA] Sometimes she has
to reconsider her choices...
It's not as though she can
see everything, after all.
[IZUMIKO] And all of this
is according to who?
According to Yukariko.
Don't worry.
You go ahead
and leave.
I'll protect Izumiko.
Stop messing
with his head.
Someday you're going
to push him too far!
[IZUMIKO] Come back!
Please just talk to me!
I completely understand
why you're angry...
and I'm sorry...
I know it's my fault that
Sagara said all that stuff...
He was being a total jerk.
Please, I don't want you
to avoid me because of it.
I'm not avoiding you.
It's obvious to me
what he's doing...
Even so...
he still pisses me off.
[MIYUKI] What are you doing?
[IZUMIKO] I'm just so relieved
that you're not mad at me.
[MIYUKI] You know,
you really are different
than the Hime-gami...
I wonder why that is.
I don't think I'm the
one to ask about that.
[MIYUKI] Neither is Yukimasa.
He doesn't know you
all that well...
He doesn't...
but with all we've been
through, I certainly do by now.
I'll have to
give it some thought.
[HAYAKAWA] I knew it was
coming but it still sucks.
Any race is more
entertaining when
the dark horse wins it,
but I just haven't had any
luck there today.
[KISARAGI] Hayakawa!
I would like you to explain,
clearly and completely,
why you were offering bets
on the poll outcomes.
Oh, you heard
about that?
I hear about
a lot, yes.
Technically,
it wasn't betting.
They were
popularity forecasts.
I'm allowed to have a little
fun sometimes, aren't I?
[KISARAGI] You're
not here to have fun...
[IZUMIKO] Huh. It looks like
Class 1-A got the highest score
in the booth division.
[MAYURA] Great job, everyone.
[REINA] Hey Souda,
how was the parade?
[MAYURA] The tail end of it just
reached the school grounds...
and it went off without a hitch.
[KISARAGI] Wonderful!
And now, it's time for me
to announce the results!
Congratulations!
Your class's booth
came out on top.
Which means that pretty
much everyone's attention
is now on Takayanagi...
He is the one who
conceptualized, organized,
and ran the booth.
I was well aware of
the risks when I chose
the Executive Committee...
Still, I can't help but feel
like I drew the short straw
this time around.
He'll only be favored by
other members of your class,
though, right?
It's hard to say...
It could still
go much further...
I imagine he'll be chosen to
serve as the main army's general
for the mock battle.
[BOY 3] Hey, Souda!
If you don't mind...
could you please accompany me
to the Broadcasting booth?
Me...?
What for?
[BOY 3] The Director
probably has some questions
about the parade...
Suzuhara's welcome
to tag along if she wants.
[HAYAKAWA] Well, Souda...
The parade presented by
the middle school students
was amazing...
It truly made this feel like
a Warring States Festival...!
That's obvious from
all the points it earned
in the popularity poll!
[MAYURA] Our visitors were
delighted by the parade.
The middle school students
did a great job!
[HAYAKAWA] Incidentally...
I hear you're
extremely popular among
the middle school
girls, Souda...
In fact, they see
you as a role model.
[MAYURA] Really?
And who told you that?
I know this might be
a little sudden...
but the middle schoolers have a
very special favor to ask you...
They're going to be joining
us here in just a moment.
[MAYURA] Huh?
[MIDDLE SCHOOL GIRL 3]
We wanted to say thank you
for all your help
with the parade today.
[MIDDLE SCHOOL GIRL 2] And...
We also wanted to ask
if you'd consider serving as
the Princess General for the
middle school's defending army
in tomorrow's mock battle.
[ALL]
Please say you will!
Hey, hold on a second...!
I can't agree to
something like this here!
But it's such
an interesting twist!
[MAYURA] I'm a member of
the Executive Committee!
I'm well aware...
But the princess simply must
be represented in the game.
If she isn't...
that will affect the integrity
of the entire festival!
I suppose
Suzuhara can do it
if you aren't willing to.
I see what you're doing,
so don't drag her into this.
I'll be the princess.
[HAYAKAWA] Did you
hear that, folks...?
There's one more
thing to look forward
to in tomorrow's battle...!
This broadcast
was brought to you
by Festival Director
Yoshiki Hayakawa.
It's like before
with Kisaragi...
Is there anything scarier than
a pretty lady when she's angry?
I would appreciate an
explanation for this...
Right now.
If anything, I think
my actions should have earned
your gratitude, not your anger.
[MAYURA] Why exactly
should I be grateful?
Because I can
see the future...
I know who will control
the main army tomorrow...
Ichijou Takayanagi.
Given that...
wouldn't serving as the
general of the defending army
be the best position for you?
[MAYURA] No way...
it can't be...
[HAYAKAWA] Oh yes it can
[MAYURA] Ah...!
You pulled a fast one on me...!
That was very
sneaky of my father.
[IZUMIKO] Your father?
Wait, does that mean...?
Are you actually from
Togakushi, Director Hayakawa?
This is the first time
I've understood the saying,
"If you want to deceive the
enemy, you should start by
deceiving your allies."
But deception or not, thank you.
You are now officially
the Princess General, Souda...
That said...
all I can do is set the stage.
Your opponent has
surely set some sort
of trap on campus...
Be careful.
Oh, I will be.
[IZUMIKO] Mayura...?
Isn't it exciting
that you're going to--
Masumi?!
Guil-ty!
[IZUMIKO] What are
you doing here...?
Mayura and Manatsu
haven't summoned you yet.
Whether they
summon me or not,
I am always there with them...
You look cute with
your hair like that.
Sorry, I can't help myself.
When I see you, I get the
uncontrollable urge to flirt!
You haven't changed
a bit since Togakushi...!
Does that mean that
your relationship with
Mayura and Manatsu is
still the same as ever, too?
I don't understand.
What do you mean by that?
[IZUMIKO] Do you still
love them like you did
before what happened?
[MASUMI] Oh...
I think I get it.
[IZUMIKO] It's easy
to understand, really...
When we love somebody...
we want to be around them.
We want to know about them
and how they're doing.
Suzuhara, do you
have a boyfriend?
No, I don't...
Why do you ask?
Help me
with something...
Let's say I found some wandering
souls, and I thought...
"They can't stay like this.
They're suffering.
They would be better off
if I consumed them."...
That would count as
a type of love, right?
[IZUMIKO] I'm not so sure
[MASUMI] If I accept them and
offer to become one with them,
doesn't that say something
about how I feel...?
Doesn't it mean I love
them after a fashion?
I guess, maybe...
If you're welcoming them into
yourself out of compassion
for their suffering, I suppose
that could be seen as love.
[MASUMI] That's
good to hear...!
I'm glad I had
that right...
I was having a really hard
time following Mayura...
but I feel much
better now.
[IZUMIKO] Mayura?
There was dissonance
between us...
but now I think
it was nothing big.
What do you mean
by dissonance?
[MASUMI] Isn't Shinkou coming
over for a strategy meeting...?
I should take off for now.
When the other two
summon me, I like to make
a grand entrance.
It's more fun that way...
One more thing...
I can sense the presence
of a curse here on campus...
but don't you worry.
I can disperse it
quickly enough.
Wait, Masumi!
A curse?
♪
[IZUMIKO] Please stay away...
You have to...
or we're all doomed.