♪
[STUDENTS play]
[HARUNA] So do you and Sagara
sleep in the same room
now that he's
staying at the shrine?
Of course not...!
His room is out in the lodge...
We do eat together, though.
Yeah...?
That must be nice.
Well, it's not exactly
like guys of his caliber
come along every day,
you know what I mean?
[AYUMI] Why don't
you ask him out?
[HARUNA] I'd have
too many rivals.
Surely he'll try out for
one of the sports teams.
He's just so athletic...!
Y'know...?
I wonder if he'd
be willing to have
his ride pick him
up a little later
so he could join
the basketball team.
Aww...
Great, so you're
after him, too?
[AYUMI] Now you're
being paranoid...
What do you think, Izumiko?
I doubt he'll join
any of the teams.
When we go home...
he spends the
rest of the day
practicing with
Nonomura.
What is he
practicing?
[IZUMIKO] He's
doing archery.
No way, for real?!
That's so cool!
I wanna see Sagara draw a bow!
Do you think he'll come
with the rest of the
class on the fieldtrip?
[AYUMI] Yeah, why wouldn't he?
[HARUNA] What do you think
he'll do during free time...?
Hang out with
Misaki and the guys?
What about you?
Think you'll be coming?
Huh?
[AYUMI] We were talking
about the fieldtrip.
[IZUMIKO] I don't think
I have a choice, do I?
[HARUNA] Jeez...!
Could you sound
less enthusiastic?
Just wait...
I know you'll have a good time!
[AYUMI] I swear, you're more
tense than anyone else I know...
You should try
relaxing sometime.
--[YOHEI] Hey!
--[AYUMI] Ow!
[AYUMI] Watch where
you're going, Yohei!
[WAMIYA] Am I interrupting?
[IZUMIKO] Hi, Wamiya...
[WAMIYA] You haven't quite
been yourself lately.
Oh...
You don't think so?
[WAMIYA] Not since that new
transfer student came.
Really?
[WAMIYA] I was
wondering if you hate him.
Yes, I do.
[WAMIYA] I thought
that was the case...
That's how I feel.
Y'know, I think
we should go to
Sototsugawa High
School together...
So what do you say?
Uh...
yeah...
[IZUMIKO] Hi, I'm home!
Welcome back.
A package came for you
when you were at school.
It's from Yukariko.
From Mother?
[SAWA] Oh, my.
What an adorable cell phone...
And you were needing
a new one, right...?
That's nice of her.
What does your mother
have to say...?
Is she still doing well?
[IZUMIKO] I'm running
over to the lodge.
What about your tea?
[IZUMIKO] Sagara!
Never startle an archer!
I thought my mother
might be able
to do something
about all this...
Maybe she could help you, too.
That letter's
from her?
[MIYUKI] Well, if Yukimasa
was going to obey anyone...
it would be Yukariko
or nobody at all.
What should I do?
About what?
She says she wants
me to meet her while
we're on the
fieldtrip in Tokyo...
But I can't go.
Yeah? Why not?
Because I can't handle
being somewhere so crowded...
I couldn't even
go to Career Day.
I got sick just
thinking about it.
Well?
What do you expect
me to do about it...?
This is
confidential stuff...
She explicitly
said not to tell
anyone from school.
It's a weird request...
but I don't see how you
can refuse to do it.
She told me to contact
her using this...
The problem is...
Well, I can't send
text messages.
[MIYUKI] Why not?
The phone will break.
[MIYUKI] What?
Computers and cell phones
all go haywire
whenever I touch them...
but there's no turning back
if I break this one.
You're actually being
serious about this,
aren't you...?
Are you telling me
you lived your entire
life unable to
use a computer
or a phone?
[IZUMIKO] I have
used a phone...!
Just not a cell...
Ah, man, it's
like you're
living in the
Stone Age.
[IZUMIKO] Sagara, please...
I want you to take
this cell phone and
go see my mother for me.
[MIYUKI] You want me to what?
This may be the only
chance we get.
We can't waste it...
and besides...
You'd probably be better at
winning her over than I would.
Oh, come on...
Why are you trying to dump all
of this onto my shoulders?
Isn't she going out of
her way to arrange this
because she wants to see you...?
What if I went by myself
and she didn't show?
So then maybe
I do have to go...
but will you please
come with me?
Since this is obviously
so important to you,
I'm willing to do what I can.
All right.
Then so am I.
Huh...?
Wamiya?
He said he wasn't coming.
He isn't really the
type of person who goes
on fieldtrips and stuff.
Now that I think of it he's
kind of like you, I guess.
I didn't realize that.
Ya want any?
Hey, what's the matter?
You airsick?
It's behind me...
[AYUMI] Is there
something in the back?
It's nothing...
I'll be okay.
[HARUNA] You okay...?
You look pale.
[IZUMIKO] Haruna...
would you mind
getting my luggage?
[HARUNA] No problem, but
you don't look so good.
I'll see if I can
find you some medicine.
[MIYUKI] Hey.
Are you really sick
or are you just faking...?
We aren't due to meet up with
your mom for a while yet.
I'll be okay.
Did you send her a text?
[MIYUKI] Yeah...
She already sent a response...
Here, look.
3:30 at the northern
observatory...
But do you think
you'll actually make it?
You do look pretty pale.
[IZUMIKO] No...
I'm going.
I think I'll be okay, really,
I just need to adjust
to them, that's all.
[MIYUKI] The crowds here
in the big, bad city
are making you feel sick...?
Is that what this is about?
Don't make it sound
like I'm being a baby...
There are so many
weird things here.
They scare me.
What "weird things"
are you talking about?
Bad things that
follow me wherever I go...
They look like smoky shadows...
Sinister black figures.
If those things
actually do exist,
You can ask Yukariko
how to deal with them.
[NAKAMURA] Okay...!
I'm giving you
some free time now.
Meet back here at four...
and don't leave the Metropolitan
Government Office Building...
Everyone got that?
[STUDENTS] Yes!
Hey, do you
feel up to
visiting the
observatory?
I think so.
That one goes to the
southern observatory.
I knew you were going
to screw this up.
She specifically
said the northern one.
Well, it's already
half past three.
So you're terrified
of strangers.
Is that what this is?
You think anyone you
don't know is a threat.
They're all out to get you.
I don't think
everybody is that way.
But...
I was telling the truth
about the black figures.
[phone vibrates]
It's no good...
It looks like she
can't make it, after all.
[IZUMIKO] She can't...?!
Why not?
[MIYUKI] "Leave the
observatory immediately...
They've already found you."...?
Who's found us?
[IZUMIKO]
The creatures I mentioned.
They might be
after Mother, as well.
[MIYUKI] Yeah, right!
Come on!
We need to get out of
here, like she said!
[phone vibrating]
She wants us to go
to her house...?!
No way!
I can't go there!
Okay, I pulled up
the address she gave us.
It's not too far from here.
Are you serious?
No, we can't!
You want to see
her, don't you...?
We've come this far.
[dings]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER]
Attention, travelers...
The gates at the western
entrance are no longer
in service...
I repeat...
the gates at the
western entrance are
no longer in service.
[emergency bell]
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Attention all travelers.
The emergency bell is
a notification that all
train services--
[MIYUKI] What the hell
is going on here...?
It's almost like someone is
trying to stop us from leaving!
They may have
found us already.
Who exactly is this
"they" you keep talking about?!
I wouldn't be so scared
if I knew the answer.
But I feel someone...
and he's getting closer!
[MIYUKI] Let's get off...
We can't afford to wait here.
[footsteps, heavy breathing]
[MIYUKI] Come on, we need to
find a place that sells hats.
If we don't do something
about those braids,
you'll stand out wherever we go.
You may be right,
but even so...
[MIYUKI] Hurry!
[car door opening, closing]
[MIYUKI] Crap!
It looks like he dropped
us off at the wrong place.
[IZUMIKO] What?
[MIYUKI] We're just a couple
of blocks off, though.
We can probably walk
there in ten minutes.
[street light buzzes,
thunder rolls]
Talk about
bad timing.
It looks like it's
about to pour...
Let's hurry up.
[rain pours]
[thunder]
You've lived in the
mountains all your life,
and a little lightning
frightens you?
It's not
the lightning.
Then what, are you still scared
of whoever's looking for you?
[thunder]
That's a first.
I've never seen
someone who's
actually trembling
in fear before.
[IZUMIKO] He...
He's almost here.
[thunder]
[street lights buzzing]
At this point, even
I'm starting to think
that there might be
something out there...
Hey, I'll tell you what:
if you think it would
make you feel better, I could
chant a mantra for you.
A mantra?
[MIYUKI] I was thinking
the "evil be gone" one...
I studied them
a bit at Mt. Haguro.
[IZUMIKO] I doubt that will
chase whoever this is away...
But...
if you don't mind...
Can-
Can I please
hold your hand?
[MIYUKI] Huh?
[IZUMIKO] Earlier...
that made me feel
not quite as afraid.
[thunder]
[MIYUKI] She's so cold...
Here he comes...
It's time.
[MALE VOICE] Protect
this land from harm.
Bring it peace and safety.
Fish in the sea, grass on
the ground, birds in the sky:
may the heavens
protect them all.
Shelter them and
strengthen them;
comfort them and care for them.
Hold them and keep them always.
Be they weak or strong, wise or
foolish: guard the souls of men.
Shelter them and
strengthen them;
comfort them and
care for them...
[MIYUKI] Shield us from
the evil that walks abroad,
give us light in the darkness
that our steps may not falter...
Hide us from that
which would destroy...
Protect us from that which
would harm, lend us strength
and determination as our
feet tread your path...
Shield us from the evil that
walks abroad, give us light
in the darkness that
our steps may not falter...
Hide us from that
which would destroy.
Protect us from that
which would harm.
Lend us strength
and determination
as our feet tread your path.
[thunder]
[YUKIMASA] What do
you think you're doing,
directing that mantra at me...?
Izumiko here is the one
who's in need of an exorcism.
Sagara, it's you!
But what are
you doing he--
[MIYUKI] Hold on...!
Stay right there...!
Not one step further until you
prove you're the real Yukimasa.
You're starting to make
a fool of yourself...
Just look...
Izumiko clearly recognizes
I am who I say I am.
But just a
second ago you
were terrified
of him!
You wanna explain
that to me?
Yeah, I know...
I was scared, but this
really is Sagara...
I guess I was imagining
things, like you said.
The whole time
I was frightened
for no good reason.
Don't give me
that crap!
[YUKIMASA] Actually, the fact
she was afraid of me is proof
that I am who I claim to be.
I really, truly
felt something...
I don't know what,
exactly, but...
I could sense something
bad approaching.
[YUKIMASA] I don't
doubt that you did...
You probably sensed someone
other than just me.
There is any number of people
in the world who would like
to make you theirs.
[MIYUKI] Okay...
but we kept being blocked
from getting to Yukariko...
Were you the one behind that?
No, none of that
was my doing...
Just so you know, you won't
see her even if you do
go to her house.
She gave up on your
meeting when she was unable
to reach the
northern observatory.
Even so...
the house has a
barrier around it,
which makes it an
ideal place to rest.
[IZUMIKO sneezes]
[IZUMIKO] Mother
really isn't here...
Is she?
[YUKIMASA] You mustn't
hold it against her...
She thought it would be best if
she acted as a decoy to draw
their attention away from you.
I guess I should
be used to it by now.
Mother's job in public security
always keeps her busy.
Taking that job
was wise on her part...
Though Yukariko's aptitude
is also some of what
keeps her busy...
Now, Izumiko, go upstairs and
look for a change of clothes...
And feel free to rest
for a little bit...
You look like you're about
to fall asleep standing up.
[YUKIMASA] Don't go
taking your pants off.
Keep in mind, this is
somebody else's home.
Where would I be
without you here
to point out the obvious?
[YUKIMASA] You're always
so angry when I see you.
Have you ever thought
we might try to have
a polite conversation
when we're alone?
[MIYUKI] It just pisses me off
how you're always so damn smug.
You might've fooled Suzuhara
but you can't fool me...
I know what
you're really like...
And don't forget it.
What are you
talking about now?
[MIYUKI] I saw it
with my own eyes:
Suzuhara was literally
shaking with fear...
She went back to normal
the second you showed up,
but only because of a spell...
I know what you did:
you exorcised her!
[YUKIMASA] So what?
I bet you're the reason
Yukariko decided not
to show up today.
I bet she could
sense your presence!
Yes, well, that
was inevitable...
You may not know
this yet, but it's
in their nature to run.
Like I told Izumiko earlier,
there is an endless list
of people who want to use
her powers for their
own personal gain.
Businessmen...
politicians...
academics...
men of religion...
even us Mountain Monks.
What type of power
does she have that would
attract so much interest?
[YUKIMASA] Don't you see...?
All that interest is
proof of its rarity...
Fewer and fewer people are
born with the pure power
that Mountain Monks train
all their lives to obtain.
This power has been given only
to women since ancient times.
A power given only to women?
I don't get it...
She certainly doesn't
seem all that impressive...
She's just a big scaredy cat who
can't do anything on her own.
[YUKIMASA] True...
I can't say that
she's fully awoken yet.
I'm sick of
this crap...
If you really want to
protect Suzuhara so badly,
do it yourself.
There is no way
in hell I'm going to work
as your lackey...!
If I have to, I'll find a way
to see Yukariko myself and--
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara...?
You should have warned us
you were coming down.
Suzuhara...?
[YUKIMASA] Get away from her.
Now...!
You're not dressed to stand in
the presence of Her Highness...
Get back!
[HIME-GAMI] Oh...
Yukimasa...
You are here, too?
I apologize for
welcoming you in such
an unseemly manner...
I had not yet made
arrangements to receive you.
Please, forgive me.
[HIME-GAMI] All is well...
I am the one who arrived
without announcing my intent.
This is my first time
descending into Izumiko.
I have not yet
adjusted to this body...
It is rather unpleasant, as it
is still too young for me...
Despite that...
[HIME-GAMI] I have come...
because I sensed something
monumental taking wing.
[YUKIMASA] Highness.
Will you stay with
Izumiko henceforth?
[HIME-GAMI] Let us
not be hasty...
It is not as though
you have caught me yet...
Regardless...
I would advise you to take
good care of Izumiko's body...
You must look after it well.
This child will likely
serve as my last vessel.
It will come to a
close as soon as that?
[HIME-GAMI] It may...
I doubt I will go
beyond this generation.
Princess!
[IZUMIKO] What?!
W-w-why am I wearing this...?
I'm...
I...
Hush.
Calm down.
You don't have to
remember everything now...
It will come back to you
gradually over time.
Uh, I...
Have to go.
So you're telling me she's
from a line of women who
are susceptible to possession?
I thought
I was prepared.
I had already
assumed that Izumiko
was a very
special child...
but I never
considered this.
[MIYUKI] What are
you talking about?
You were right...
Just as you said, protecting
Izumiko will go far beyond
what you are capable of.
If that's the case, then--
I hereby rescind my order
for you to attend
the same school as Izumiko...
If you want to transfer,
feel free to choose any
school you like.
Wait, what...?!
Just like that?
What is going
on here?
Shouldn't you be
at least a little happier...?
This is what you wanted, right?
♪
[MIYUKI] There aren't any
students named Wamiya.
[IZUMIKO] That's impossible!