♪
[MIYUKI] Hey!
[MAYURA] It's
nothing personal...
Sorry.
[MIYUKI] It's nothing personal?
Seriously?
Take a moment
to look around you...
We're outside reality here.
We've entered a different plane.
One of these
beings is Masumi...
Can you tell which one?
Consider all of the
others his followers...
They can't do much on their own,
but I bet it would still hurt
if they attacked.
[MIYUKI] I don't understand
why you're doing this!
[MAYURA] I suggest you
act quickly if you don't
want to get hurt.
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara
can't defend herself!
You don't need
to worry about her...
I'll see she that
comes to no harm.
Shelter me...!
Cloak me in protective armor!
I warned you, didn't I?
Act quickly or suffer.
I just want to know the
extent of what you've learned
in your training.
Youkai demons!
I can't fight these!
[MAYURA] Still being shy?
You have two options...
Catch Masumi...
or find your way back to
the real world by breaking
through his barrier.
That's enough, Mayura!
Please, don't do this!
Exorcisms should be
simple for a Mountain Monk!
But I need a staff
for an exorcism!
[MANATSU] Ask and
ye shall receive.
This is dangerous!
Put a stop to it, Mayura!
You're gonna be all right.
Don't worry.
I don't mean me...!
I mean Sagara!
I don't understand you.
Don't you want to see
what he's capable of...?
You told me he's
kept you in the dark.
Aren't you tired of that?
That's incredible...
Didn't they tell
you anything when
you enrolled?
That's Sagara...
He doesn't tell
anyone everything...
Not even me.
[MAYURA] From everything
you said, it sounded like
you weren't satisfied
with your partnership.
[IZUMIKO] That's not it...!
I was just venting before...
It's my fault he's been
dragged into this world.
If not for me, he could
be living a normal life.
So it's not surprising
that he finds me annoying.
Miyuki, listen to me...!
Masumi is right next to you!
That isn't Manatsu!
[MANATSU]
That's enough, Mayura...
You took it too far.
[MAYURA] You think so?
[MANATSU] You don't
get it, do you...?
I bet you think they're gonna
shrug the whole thing off
with a laugh.
Just because you're
a girl or something.
Not because I'm a girl.
Because I'm me.
[MANATSU] That really
sucked, didn't it?
My body feels
like it's going numb.
[MANATSU] Masumi threw you
back to this plane.
He wasn't gentle...
It was right after
Suzuhara identified him.
[MIYUKI] The one who
gave me the staff...
that was Masumi...?
Where's Suzuhara?
[IZUMIKO cries]
[MASUMI] What's wrong?
What are you crying about?
[IZUMIKO] I'm really
upset with myself.
Yeah? Why's that?
[IZUMIKO] All this time...
and I couldn't see.
What are you
talking about?
You saw me.
[IZUMIKO] No, that's
not what I meant...
I just realized
how blind I've been.
I was so scared.
Mayura was just testing
Shinkou's abilities.
She kept you safe and sound
like she said she would, right?
I was still scared...!
It's not like it being
a test changes that!
[MASUMI] Well, we were
trying to be threatening.
I figured you could
handle it, though.
I thought you were
braver than this, honestly.
[IZUMIKO] It's not just me.
I got Sagara involved...
I'm screwing up his life...
That's what I finally
realized today.
But I still don't
want to admit that
I'm expecting anything of him.
That's why I was so
negative about him when
I talked to Mayura.
Okay, so...
Is that what's going on?
Shinkou's the one who's
got you down in the dumps?
[IZUMIKO] No matter how
badly I want to be normal...
I know that's not
going to happen.
But if it wasn't for me, Sagara
could be a normal person with
a normal life
and normal friends.
[MASUMI scoffs]
You know, you really
shouldn't bully
people like this.
It's mean.
[MASUMI] Now it's my fault?
It seems like you're
perking up a bit...
Pretty soon now you may
actually notice where you are.
[IZUMIKO] Huh?
[MASUMI] When you have a
naturally loose grip on reality,
it's very easy to get lost...
particularly around these parts.
What should I do?
[MASUMI] You'll be fine...
I'll send you back...
It's not every day I meet
somebody who can see me...
It's important for me
to look out for you.
--[MSF 1] Suzuhara!
--[MSF 2] Are you out there?
--[MSF 3] Can you hear us?
--[MSF 4] Suzuhara!
Hello? Izumiko...!
Where did you run off to?
[MSF 1] Are you all right?
[MAYURA] Whoa...!
How long have you
been standing there?
[IZUMIKO] Uh...
well...
I...
[MSF 1]
Izumiko Suzuhara, I presume?
It's such a pleasure
to meet you...
It really is an honor to
actually get to talk to you
in person.
Huh...?
Uh, what...?
[MSF 1] Sorry...
I don't blame you
for being confused...
You're quite famous
in our little group...
but I'm sure you have
no idea who we are.
So let's change that...
I guess I should prob'ly
introduce myself first...
My name is Mizuhiko Ryougoku,
and I'm the acting president
of the History Society.
[RYOUGOKU] As I'm sure
you're already aware,
the History Society also serves
as Mayura Soda's fan club...
It's only natural that
we would know a great deal
about her roommate.
But I sure hope
we can...
I assume they're here
under your orders,
since they're
your groupies.
They don't know anything
about Masumi, okay...?
He simply used them
to set the stage.
Now...
My methods were rough,
I'll admit that...
and I'm sorry...
But the History Society
definitely made an impression
on you and Izumiko, didn't it?
[RYOUGOKU] As a matter of fact,
we plan to do a presentation
on ninja at the
school festival...
I'd love it if the
two of you joined us.
So just give it
some thought, okay?
[MIYUKI] Wait...
Are you really asking us
to join the MSF?
I want to remain
a bystander...
I much prefer to work
alongside president Kisaragi.
[MAYURA] And you
really think that's
in Izumiko's best interest?
It's not like it's my place
to tell her what to do...
She can make her own choices.
[RYOUGOKU] I look forward
to seeing you again when
September rolls around.
[RYOUGOKU] Take care.
Well, that's that, huh?
Our question's been answered.
Shinkou is a newbie,
through and through...
Looks like Dad was way
off base this time around.
It would have been
a lot easier if you had
just listened when
I told you that.
Yeah, I guess you've
got a point there.
But I can see
why Mayura thought our dad
was right about you...
Masumi, Takayanagi's
shiki-- none of the stuff
that's happened has
freaked you out at all.
Just because I don't
scream and cry about it
doesn't mean
I'm not freaked out.
[MANATSU] Whatever the
situation, it always feels like
you'll pull through
it on your own.
Although, this time
around it was Suzuhara
who wrapped things up.
Y'know, sometimes it seems
like everybody in her life
is using her for some
reason or another...
Makes me wonder why she never
notices it when it's happening.
[phone vibrates]
[MANATSU] It's from Mimura.
[MAYURA] What is it?
[MANATSU] It- It's Tabi...
He's not doing well...
Mimura says to
come quickly if I can.
Tabi's sick?
I need to go
as soon as possible.
[MAYURA] Hold on...
If you're leaving,
I'll come with you.
Me, too.
You said you were going
to introduce me to Tabi.
Uh-uh...
It's best for me to go
by myself if he's that sick.
Besides, Mayura, you have to
stay here and host the trip.
Another time, okay...?
I promise you can meet Tabi
when he's feeling better.
More than anything else, sick
animals need peace and quiet.
[MAYURA] You're
really going to leave
in the middle of our trip...?
For a horse?
[MANATSU] Tabi's more
important than a field trip.
[MAYURA] I can't let
you go by yourself...
Wait until tomorrow.
We can go together.
No, I'm going...
I owe Tabi that much,
at the very least...
It shouldn't really affect
the trip at all if I slip out
on my own today...
You still have Masumi.
Is that really
what you're planning?
To have him fill in for you?
[MANATSU] He's been dying
to experience school life...
This trip should be the
perfect opportunity for that.
[MAYURA] What are you saying?
[MANATSU] Mayura,
this is Togakushi...!
You know Masumi can handle it.
What are you thinking...?
You're scaring me, Manatsu.
[MAYURA] Masumi?
[MASUMI] I hear there's a
student council meeting
going on!
I hope we can play nice...
And please don't hold
that little scuffle
earlier against me...
I don't have that many friends,
and I'd hate to lose one because
of something as silly as this.
Are you going to make
things appear and disappear
on this plane, too?
No, of course not.
I'm going to be the
best Manatsu I can be...
and I think you can
help me with that.
We are roomies,
after all, right...?
You can tell me everything
you've observed about Manatsu...
and I can use that as
reference for how to behave.
Look...
I know I'm not in any position
to ask you for favors...
but would you mind
looking after Masumi?
Wow, that has got
to be the meekest
I've ever seen you
act before, Souda.
[MAYURA] Don't make fun of me!
Manatsu is always saying that
no matter what's going on,
we should try to
make Masumi happy...
He's sticking by that belief,
doing something to please Masumi
even though he's so
worried about Tabi.
Whatcha doin'?
And I'm supposed to act
like everything's normal?
This'll be great.
[MASUMI laughs]
[MASUMI] I'm so excited...!
I hardly ever get to do this!
[MAYURA] Oh, really...?
Okay, I understand...
Just be sure to tell
Manatsu to give me a call
whenever he can...
Yes, please do.
Thanks so much.
It's Tabi...
He can't even stand...
He's had colic before, but it's
never been as bad as this...
The other times he was
still able to get up.
[IZUMIKO] So this is
really serious, then?
Yes, I think it is...
This is gonna
crush Manatsu...
He can't draw the line
between people and horses.
[IZUMIKO] I'm so sorry.
[MAYURA] It's hard
to describe...
but in a way, Manatsu
and Masumi have always
balanced each other out.
Neither one of them acts as
a balance for me, though.
[IZUMIKO] Balance how?
[MAYURA] Emotionally.
[MAYURA] With Masumi so
cheerful, Manatsu must be...
[MASUMI] Found you!
Found you...!
It's not every day that we're
all under the same roof.
Shouldn't we be
spending time together?
Oh honestly!
Do you really think
you can pass for Manatsu?
I sure do...!
But I'm allowed to have some
fun of my own while I'm here,
aren't I?
Well, this is going
to be interesting.
[MIYUKI] Can you tell how your
siblings are doing even when
you're not in the same place?
[MASUMI] Nope, it
doesn't work that way.
Can you instinctively
tell what they've been doing?
Yeah, whenever
I can look at them.
What about telepathy?
Can you read their minds?
Like, for example...
Can you tell me what
Souda's thinking right now?
[MASUMI] Things would be a
whole lot easier if I could.
[REINA] What are
you doing in here?
This is the girls' room.
[MAYURA] Sorry about that.
[MIYUKI] We're
leaving right now.
[KISARAGI] You have good timing.
There's something I would like
to tell everybody after dinner.
Could you please tell
the guys that we're
meeting in the parlor?
[KISARAGI] Good evening.
Akinokawa and I have prepared
a performance that all of you
need to see.
[KISARAGI] Please understand...
as Student Body President,
it is my job to protect
the Student Council.
That is the
purpose of my dance.
One in our midst...
has been possessed...
Something not human
walks among us...
I shall dance in order
to protect you from
that vile spirit.
Just as in the myth of
Ame no Uzume no Mikoto...
the tale that tells of this
mountain's beginnings...
dance has the power to purify.
[IZUMIKO] That's incredible.
She's so strong.
[SHIBATA] Whoa, what happened?
[BOY 1] Hey!
[HOSHINO] Check the breaker!
[SHIBATA] Ouch!
[BOY 2] We must have
flashlights somewhere!
That was awesome.
Like something out
of a horror movie.
You know, we could
totally use something
like that in the festival.
Hey, wait...
Souda's brother is gone!
[OKOCHI] Yeah. Hey...
Sagara's missing, too.
[KISARAGI] What...?
Why would he vanish?
Guys, we should send
somebody to go look for them.
But where could
they have gone?
How should I know?
[IMAI] Crap...
[OKOCHI] Let's split up
and search all the rooms.
[SHIBATA] Maybe we should.
[HOSHINO] H-Hey, who's there?
Were you chilled
to the bone...?
We got you good.
[BOYS laugh]
[MASUMI] You guys look pale!
[MIYUKI] Somebody had
to do it, you know...?
Or the president would
have been disappointed.
[SHIBATA] You jerks!
[OKOCHI] You really
had us going there.
Come on, Reina.
We should go
get changed...
You can leave now.
The show's over.
I think I'm gonna
hit the baths again.
I just want to
get some sleep.
What happened
in there?
Did Kisaragi actually
repel Masumi?
Yes, I think she did...
But as long as
he's in Togakushi,
he's still stronger
than she is.
What I don't
understand is
why you were
repelled with him.
I was sort of...
tagging along.
She's on the phone.
Think she's talking to Manatsu?
[MAYURA] That's it.
We'll probably
lose Tabi tonight.
[MIYUKI yawns] Souda's not up?
She needs all
the rest she can get...
She was awake all night
waiting for the call...
Where's Masumi?
He's still sleeping...
or he's playing possum.
I wonder if you and
I should go check on Manatsu
and see how he's
dealing with all this.
[IZUMIKO] Yeah...
That's a good idea.
He really shouldn't
be alone right now.
Don't be ridiculous!
Of course I'm going with you!
Did you seriously
think I would stay behind?
If there's anybody who
should talk to him, it's me.
Do you really think so?
Even if you do go, it's not
like you guys are gonna see
the situation in
the same light...
I mean, you're not going to
be all that broken up about it
if Tabi dies, are you?
[MAYURA] How can you say that?
Of course I'll be sad about it!
[MASUMI] Whatever you say...
But it seems to me you'd
be better off staying
here than bothering him...
He doesn't want to see you...
I do...
So hang out with me.
Oh, I see where this is going.
You're prioritizing his
feelings over mine...
When did you start
siding with Manatsu?
[MASUMI] You know how it works.
When you and Manatsu stop seeing
the world in the same way,
my time as Masumi will end.
[MIYUKI] Is that one of
the conditions, then?
The two of you have to share
the exact same image of Masumi
in order for him
to remain embodied?
[MAYURA] Yeah, pretty much...
Our willpower is all
that makes this work...
I guess I can let Manatsu
have his way until he's had
some time to grieve.
We'll go in your
place, so please try not
to worry.
We'll bring him back...
Everything will be okay,
you'll see.
[MAYURA] Okay.
If you insist...
I'd appreciate it.
[MIYUKI] Excuse me...!
Is Manatsu Souda here?
We came to see him.
We're his friends.
Friends of his, huh?
He should be back in the barn,
cleaning things up...
Would you like me
to get him for you?
How, uh...
how's Tabi?
Tabi passed away...
this morning, actually...
The recovery services
left only a moment ago.
How awful...
That truck we passed...
[IZUMIKO] Hi, Manatsu.
Oh, hey...
You guys came...?
I'm sorry it was a wasted trip.
I can't introduce you
to Tabi now.
Why don't you
tell us about him?
[MANATSU] He was a dark bay...
so his coat was
practically black...
The bottom of his legs
were white, though...
The very bottom...
almost like he
was wearing socks.
So, what was his
personality like?
[MANATSU] It did change
some over the years...
He was pretty fierce back
when we were little kids.
I don't know how many times
he bucked me and Masumi off.
[IZUMIKO] He had
a long life, didn't he?
[MANATSU] Sometimes the owner
decides how long a horse lives.
If a horse can't
stand, it quickly grows
weaker and weaker.
When it can't move, its
own weight presses down
on its organs...
Necrosis sets in...
It's an agonizing way to die.
So when he passed away this
morning, it was because---
[MANATSU] I gave him
a shot to stop his heart...
I made the call
to euthanize him.
Man, I'm so sorry.
[MANATSU] It's possible
he could have lived.
There are treatments
we could've tried...
but I decided to let him
find some peace.
[MIYUKI] You didn't want
Souda to come here...
Is that why?
[MANATSU] Yeah...
She's been really
worried about you, you know.
[MANATSU] Sure...
But Masumi's fine, right...?
This was a great
opportunity for him...
Plus...
it gave me some time to think.
Humans have the ability
to put things to an end
rather than simply accept
whatever fate happens to have
in store for them.
At some point,
Mayura will be alone...
She won't get to spend her
entire life with Masumi...
or me...
Masumi and I get that...
but not Mayura.
She still doesn't seem
to understand it.
Why are you talking
like this, Manatsu?
I have this sick feeling
that the time has come
to put everything to an end...
soon, while I'm still able to...
Anything would be better
than leaving her alone.
[MAYURA] What are you
going to put to an end?
Well, Manatsu...?!
Spell it out!
What have you decided
it's time to put an end to?!
Why are you here?
Why did you leave him...?
I didn't want you
to choose me, so why?!
Masumi isn't
hurting right now...
Of course I'm going to choose
to be with the brother
who's in pain...!
It's only natural!
Slow down...
Take a moment to realize
just how sad you are.
No, you're wrong!
I'm not sad about Tabi's death.
That would be an insult
to his memory...!
If I'm sad, it's because of what
his death has made me realize.
I have to act now
or accept my fate.
You're the person
I care most about.
But you can't care
about me the most.
Not anymore, not now!
Wait!
[IZUMIKO] Manatsuuuuuu!
♪
[MANATSU] "I haven't
changed my mind...
I've got to try...
If I became the
same thing as Masumi...
then maybe I would be
able to stay with you."
Wait, what the matter?
Is that you, Dad...?!
Please, you have to hurry!
It's Masumi...
he's going to take
Manatsu away from me!
[IZUMIKO] Am I being selfish?
Is it wrong of me to want
to be like everyone else?