[explosion]
[STUDENTS freaking out]
What do you think
just happened?
[MAYURA] Masumi...
he left me...
What's going on...?
Is it Manatsu?
The battery's dead...?
No way!
[MIYUKI] same here!
[BOY STUDENT 1] I wonder
what's up with this.
[GIRL STUDENT 1]
Why isn't it working?
[BOY STUDENT 2] Maybe
there's radio interference?
[BOY STUDENT 3] Man, my
camera won't turn on, either.
[HOSHINO] Oh, crap!
Where's Kisaragi now?
[SHIBATA] I think she's
at the riding grounds.
[MIYUKI] I'm going on patrol.
I'll start there.
Computers and cell
phones all go haywire
whenever I touch them...
[NONOMURA] Miyuki!
Nonomura, hey!
Do you think all this
might have something to do
with Suzuhara?
I only wish I could
say for certain...
I knew beforehand something
was going to happen today.
But the consequences...?
It has to be connected
to the Hime-gami, doesn't it?
Izumiko will
awaken today...
So says the prophecy
about this festival.
The prophecy...
So the Hime-gami said that
while possessing Yukariko?
[NONOMURA] That's right.
You should
take this with you.
Thank you, I will.
[MANATSU] Shinkou!
What's going on?
What was that...?
Was it Takayanagi?
Hold on one second...
You aren't Masumi...
are you?
No, Masumi
isn't here.
Suzuhara is with
Takayanagi...
I'm headed to the riding
grounds, where they are...
I want to know what's happening.
I'll come, too...
I'm worried about
the horses.
[OKOCHI] What the heck...?
What am I supposed to do now?
[MIYUKI] That's weird.
[MANATSU] An Onmyouji spell?
[MIYUKI and MANATSU]
Shelter me!
Cloak me in protective armor!
[GIRL 1] What the--?
[BOY 1] Hey...
[MIYUKI] What are
you two doing here?
Where did Suzuhara go...?
Where did
Takayanagi take her...?
Tell me!
And where in the world
did this dog come from?
[TAKAYANAGI] Watch your tone!
Wait, that voice...
You're Takayanagi!
[TAKAYANAGI] Of course I am...!
And I will not be referred
to as a lowly cur!
She is gone...
Suzuhara simply vanished and
entered another plane...
And look!
Look what she did
to Takayanagi!
So these are like
the planes in Togakushi?
As far as I can
tell, yes...
But we can't pass through
them without Masumi.
[MIYUKI]
Wamiya...!
Guide me to the place
where Suzuhara is!
[WAMIYA] I can take you into
the other land to find her.
But I think you should know...
she has absolutely
no desire to come back...
and there is a powerful
foe lying in wait for you.
[MIYUKI] Who?
What foe...?
and why are you making it
sound like I've already lost?
Because Masumi is there...
He's waiting on the other side.
Wait, what are
you saying?
[MANATSU] I...
I thought out of
all of us, Masumi was
the most unchangeable.
Turns out I was wrong...
He managed to find someone.
Someone he can love
besides his siblings...
Izumiko!
[IZUMIKO] Through all that...
I didn't switch places
with the Hime-gami.
Despite everything
that happened...
she wasn't the one
who saved me...
I saved myself.
Does that mean that
I've been her all along...?
Was I fooling myself
this whole time...
thinking we were
separate entities?
I can't take it...
I don't want anyone
to see me like this.
I have to stay here,
in this plane.
Then everyone will be okay...
I'll never leave...
If I don't, maybe I can
escape playing a role
in the destruction of humanity.
I wish I'd never even
seen Houjou Academy.
[rustling]
Who's there...?!
Stay away from me!
[MASUMI] And why should I?
Oh, it's just you, Masumi.
[MASUMI] You guessed it.
[IZUMIKO] Is it a good
idea to leave Mayura...?
Don't you need to be
there helping her win?
Yeah, I'm supposed
to be...
Only, I'm having a hard
time understanding her...
She doesn't mind
sacrificing herself,
and I don't
really get that.
What d'you mean?
Ultimately, Mayura has
decided to throw herself away
and donate her heart to Manatsu
so she can become one with him.
She wouldn't...!
[MASUMI] A long time ago,
the three of us made a pact
to eventually merge
our identities...
but now...
some dissonance is growing
between the other two.
[IZUMIKO] In what way?
[MASUMI] They are separately
trying to find an alternative
to becoming one
with each other...
but they each hold the other's
survival above their own.
[IZUMIKO] I'm a
little jealous...
I'm not like them, am I?
No...
I wanted to help
Mayura defeat Takayanagi
in this last battle...
but...
that won't happen.
Yeah, why not?
[IZUMIKO] Because...
I can't go back
to the academy...
Apparently I'm
not actually human.
Oh, come on.
Of course
you're human!
If that is the case...
then what am I
doing here with you?
The thing about
divine spirits is,
we reside on higher
waves than humans do...
I promise, Suzuhara,
you are human.
You were just born
with the ability to
heighten your waves...
There used to be a bunch
of people with that a bility
a long time ago, but you're
an endangered species now.
In fact, your unique
power is what makes you
utterly irresistible to me...
You see...
What I'm trying to say
is that I love you, Izumiko.
[IZUMIKO gasps]
[WAMIYA] Not good.
It seems that she's thinking
about staying there permanently.
So what, you won't
take me now?
[WAMIYA] As long as you realize
it could be a one-way ticket.
Hey, this
isn't a joke!
[WAMIYA] You don't
stand much of a chance...
Do you still want to try?
Yes, you know
I do...!
Now let's go!
[MANATSU] Wait, Shinkou!
I'm going to go
with you...!
Suzuhara came to get me out when
I was trapped in Togakushi...
It's my turn to
go after her.
No, forget it...
You need to stay
right here and help Souda...
Do you have any idea
what it would do to her
if she lost both of you?
But Masumi's
my respo--
[MIYUKI]
You are coming.
You need to
apologize to Suzuhara...
and ask her to
turn you back to normal.
[TAKAYANAGI] It does seem she
and I need to have a chat.
[MIYUKI] Come on, Wamiya...
Show us the way.
[WAMIYA] As you wish.
Here I am with
a bird and a dog...
Add a donkey and a cat
and we could head to Bremen.
[TAKAYANAGI] The bird
was a rooster...!
And I'm not a dog, thank you!
Well, which way
am I supposed to go?
[WAMIYA] Directions have
little meaning here...
So go wherever you like.
[TAKAYANAGI] Now that I
think about it, Suzuhara was
very upset about how I used
animals to create shikigami...
Could this be her
form of retaliation?
[MIYUKI] You're just
now figuring that out?
[TAKAYANAGI] Do you think we can
expect the layout of this realm
to be similar to
the academy grounds?
[MIYUKI] It would make
sense if there were
some overlap between the two.
[TAKAYANAGI] In that case...
those shapes in the distance...
They're most likely the
ghosts of Hachiouji, right?
[MIYUKI] Wamiya,
are you there...?
You don't expect us to
get past them, do you?
[WAMIYA] If you want to
continue on this futile quest,
you'll have to...
If it helps...
the ghosts will vanish
if you can get past them
and cross over the rift.
Is this
Masumi's spell?
Stick close to me if you can...
If you can't, then run like
your life depends on it.
Rin...
byou...
tou...
sha...
kai...
jin...
retsu...
zai...
zen.
Protect me
and purify me.
Guide me and deliver me.
Cloak me in
protective armor!
[TAKAYANGI] The ghosts
borrow people's mental energy
in order to take form...
They shouldn't be able
to do much harm to one
with a strong mind.
Shelter me now
and give me strength.
[WAMIYA] This isn't the
only rift to cross.
[MIYUKI] There are more?!
[WAMIYA] Your task will only
become more difficult...
not easier.
The issue is the power with
which you cross the rifts.
If you attempt to cross them
with insufficient power...
you will keep returning
to this area.
[MIYUKI] And what if we aren't
able to reach Suzuhara...?
What will happen?
[WAMIYA] That's simple...
You can just pull back.
You can give up
at any time.
You'll be free if you do...
Your pain will stop.
[MAYURA] It'll be okay...
Take deep breaths.
[MANATSU] Mayura!
[MAYURA] Manatsu?!
You're all right!
I was so worried!
Sorry...
I had to go
with Sagara.
Why?
What happened?
It looks like Suzuhara
and Masumi crossed
into another plane.
But why would
they do that?
[MANATSU] He's fallen
in love with her...
with Izumiko.
So Masumi-...
He isn't going
to be coming back?
[MANATSU] I don't know.
[MAYURA] He has to...
He promised he'd
spend the day with me.
I...
I just hate the thought
of him leaving me...
and I hate the thought
of losing you...
We haven't even settled
things with Takayanagi!
It's time to stop
fighting for the top spot...
It isn't right, the way
we've been using Masumi.
There will
be victims...
And Suzuhara might
be one of them!
So, you don't like me?
I-it's not
like that, really...
It's just, we don't
know each other very well.
[MASUMI] There is
a part of me that knows
you much better
than you think...
[IZUMIKO] To Masumi, love means
something very different.
[MASUMI] They
can't stay like this.
They're suffering.
They would be better off
if I consumed them...
That would count as
a type of love, right?
[MASUMI] I could bring so
much fun into your life...
Please!
Just let me show you!
I don't think...
I'll ever be able
to have fun again...
Everything has changed somehow.
[IZUMIKO] Is this...?
Ujitero Hojo's wife,
Ohisa, was still standing
until the castle fell.
But even so...
she was never reunited
with her husband.
There will never be such
an unhappy ending for you!
[FEMALE GHOST 1] Oh, Milady!
It's wonderful to see that
the lord has returned to you!
[FEMALE GHOST 2] We have
prepared a small celebration
in your honor.
Everyone here has
been so worried about you.
The palace is waiting...
Shall we go?
[IZUMIKO] Um...
sure.
[MASUMI] Come on!
[TAKAYANAGI] Your costume
is falling apart...
Is that significant...?
Are all of these attacks
actually hurting you?
No!
I'll be all right.
[MIYUKI] This place
doesn't actually exist,
so these injuries aren't real...
If I start to believe I've been
hurt, it will become true.
The fact I'm already
suffering means I don't fully
believe this isn't real.
But...
does that mean I don't
fully believe in Suzuhara?
[TAKAYANAGI] I'm truly
impressed with you, Sagara...
I mean it.
I sincerely admire you.
For how hard you're trying...
to bring me to Suzuhara...
so she can make things right.
[MIYUKI] Same to you.
I'm truly impressed
with your arrogance.
[TAKAYANAGI] You spoke of
the power needed to cross
the rifts...
What power did
you mean, exactly?
[WAMIYA] The power of your
belief in what you are doing.
Your belief in what
the future may hold.
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara!
Will you bear the weight of the
Hime-gami's burden alone...?
What happened to wanting
to be a normal girl?
Have you thought about
what I proposed earlier?
Souda, I can tell
we're a lot alike...
I can see the benefit of
pretending to be your fiancée...
Even so...
I don't think it's
something we should do.
But why not?
[MIYUKI] I understand
that you mean well...
and I'm certain it
would be effective...
Unfortunately, it would
also harm the people
we care most about.
[MAYURA] Okay, then...
so what now?
Hopefully...
I'll be able to discover
a path for her that nobody
has thought of before.
[MAYURA] Wait a second...
when you say that, are you
talking about Izumiko?
[WAMIYA] The power of your
belief in what you are doing.
Your belief in what
the future may hold.
[MIYUKI yelling] Izumiko...!
You have to know
that I'm here for you!
Is something
the matter?
[IZUMIKO] I think I just
heard someone call my name.
I didn't
hear anything.
[MASUMI] A cell phone
isn't going to work here.
[MIYUKI] but if you run
into trouble out there ...
don't try to handle it
all on your own, okay?
[phone rings]
Hello?
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara!
Where are you?
[IZUMIKO] Miyuki...!
[MIYUKI] Say, "Come to me!"...
and I will!
[IZUMIKO] But...
this is...
[MIYUKI] Just hurry and say it!
[IZUMIKO] Come to me, Miyuki...!
I-I-I... I need you!
[phone hangs up]
[WAMIYA] You finally called...
so I came to you...
but did you really
have to wait so long?
Wamiya?
[WAMIYA] My gain is your loss...
Suzuhara will never belong
to Togakushi or you...
Keep trying and you'll
just waste your time.
I knew he was here...!
You brought Shinkou...!
Just because he's here
doesn't mean I can't be
a good host to Suzuhara.
[WAMIYA] Don't be greedy...!
You already have the siblings.
[MASUMI] That's true.
[WAMIYA] Now, go!
I'll see you
some other time...
Bye for now, Suzuhara.
Did you really have
to chase him away like that?
[WAMIYA] I'm about to do
something extraordinary...
something I didn't
want him to watch.
[IZUMIKO] Extraordinary?
[MIYUKI pants]
[IZUMIKO gasps]
Are you
really Suzuhara?
[IZUMIKO gasps]
[MIYUKI] Izumiko?
Are you sure?
That's what
I was hoping for.
Are you okay?
It's just that I can't
handle it very well
when you're dressed up
like the Hime-gami...
It sort of makes
my head spin.
I'm sorry...
My braids came undone.
But, you know what...?
I finally realized
than I am her...
and that made me so scared...
I didn't want
anybody to see me...
I thought I'd hide
for the rest of my life.
But...
you and Wamiya being here
changes that somehow...
I feel a little better.
I need you...
to tell me that you need me.
I won't know it
if you don't tell me...
and I won't fully believe
in what I do unless I know
that you really need me.
What I said
before still stands...
I won't become
your servant, ever.
But the Hime-gami is
too heavy a burden...
You can't carry it on your own.
Let me help
you find a path...
a way to avoid becoming
the Hime-gami completely...
and destroying
all of humanity...
Just tell me!
Say that you need me!
But if I tell you that...
If you do there will
be no going back.
[staff falls]
[MANATSU] We change as
we get older, right...?
And Masumi changes
along with us...
Changing doesn't
mean disappearing.
Masumi will
come back...
and when he does we'll
see that our bond may alter
but it won't vanish.
[KISARAGI] There you are!
We've all decided we should
go ahead with the last round
of the Battle Game, as planned.
We're going around
and making sure
that everyone
knows about it.
[OKOCHI] We thought it would
be best to distract everyone
with a game.
[IZUMIKO] This
dog is Takayanagi?
I figured you did it
without realizing it.
Admit what you did...
You cast a
spell, right...?
What was in that
hot air balloon?
[TAKAYANAGI] It was an
experimental hybrid curse.
There were some hallucinogenic
chemicals mixed in, as well.
Suzuhara...
I sincerely apologize for
underestimating you...
Please turn me
back into a human!
Well...
it's not that I
don't want to...
I just don't
know if I can.
[TAKAYANAGI]
I'm stuck like this?
[WAMIYA] Don't forget,
you almost never consciously
use your powers.
You need to set
your mind free...
and to do that,
you have to dance.
[HAYAKAWA] Uh...
At this point, we are
still unable to determine
exactly what is happening.
But the games will continue...
[BOY STUDENT 1]
What's going on?
[GIRL STUDENT 1] They have
arrows coming out of them!
[BOY STUDENT 2] Are those...
ghosts?
[BOY STUDENT 3] For real?
[BOY STUDENT 4] I didn't
know ghosts could smile...
[BOY STUDENT 5]
Where are they all going?
Masumi...
I'm sorry,
Mayura, but...
Well...
I found someone else who
could see me and I had to go.
How could
you do this...?
and where is Izumiko?
Seems Shinkou found the
strength to drive me away.
She turned
you down, huh?
I don't know...
It's hard to say, but for now at
least, I'm here to defend you.
Welcome back, Masumi...
I knew you would never
really abandon me.
That's why I was
able to return.
[MAYURA] Is that Izumiko
dancing over there?
[MASUMI] You have
to watch quietly.
Suzuhara doesn't
realize we can see her...
It's better that way.
[MAYURA] She's beautiful.
I can see why
you had to go...
but I'm still
glad you came back.
[helicopter]
[YUKIMASA] It seems Izumiko's
done an excellent job dissolving
the spell on the school.
I'd say she's earned
a passing grade...
but I think the adults can
take things over from here.
You did well today...
Izumiko.
♪
[STUDENTS partying]
[HODAKA] Well.
It's safe to say that she's
Houjou Academy's top student...
but she is our World Heritage
Candidate, after all.
[IZUMIKO] So, Miyuki...
listen...
I know how I respond
to what you said earlier
is extremely important...
So I'd like to take some time...
but, still...
For as long as I live,
I'll never forget that
you came for me...
when I was almost lost for good.
[MIYUKI] Yeah...
What you said...
I know I'll carry it with me
for the rest of my life.
[IZUMIKO] Um...
Miyuki?
[MIYUKI snores]