[MAYURA] Come on, hurry...!
You're taking forever!
[MANATSU] That's 'cause
my bag is weighing me down.
[MAYURA] I told you you
should've shipped it beforehand,
like we did.
[MANATSU] Calm down.
We've still got tons of time.
That's what
you always say...
and yet somehow, you
always end up rushing.
What do you
make of her
accusations,
Shinkou...?
Sound legit?
Who...?
Shinkou...?
Me?
Where did that
come from?
Well, you
hate it when
I call you
Miyuki...
so I just
came up with
a nickname for you.
[horn]
[MAYURA] It's here!
♪
It's still hard
to believe this.
Huh...?
Believe what?
Oh, just that I'm riding
on a bullet train...
and that I'm actually going
to Nagano to see your home.
Don't forget
the last part...
The real reason
we're going is for
the Student Council's
Executive Committee.
I know. It's...
surprising...
That I belong to
the Committee, I mean.
[MAYURA] Really?
I don't think so...
You've been a big help since
you joined the Committee.
But Sagara invited
you first, didn't he...?
And then there's me.
I'm the one he threw in
as an afterthought.
[MAYURA] There's something
I've been wanting to ask you...
If you don't mind...
Why did you and
Sagara become partners?
[IZUMIKO] It was something my
father and Sagara's father
agreed upon.
[MAYURA] Family issues?
More or less...
I'm beginning to
accept it, though.
But you're
a natural pair...!
The way you guys
work together
is totally seamless.
You know...
like that time with
Takayanagi's shiki.
We're like a natural pair?
[MAYURA] Boyfriend girlfriend!
No, it isn't like that
between us at all!
[MAYURA] Sagara's quite
a catch, you know...
There are tons of girls
who're interested...
but he turns 'em down
like he's already promised.
Oh, yeah...?
well the same
could be said
of you, though.
Yeah, I don't
have any time for
a boyfriend...
You know how it is...
We've just got
more baggage than
the average person.
It's hard...
He'll never...
grow up...
And he'll never
have a girlfriend.
Can I ask when
Masumi passed away?
The fifth
of this month.
How old was he?
He was six.
We took a nap...
He was the only one
who didn't wake up...
They told us it
was heart failure.
After the funeral, we left
T'gah-kushi and moved
to Nagano...
Since then...
his name has been taboo.
I don't get it...
Doesn't he show himself
to your parents, too?
No, my mother's
just a normal woman.
Anyway!
I'm so glad you decided
to come with us...
It'll be a lot of fun.
What...?
How much longer
are you gonna be?
We're here at the pick-up spot.
Our house
is about
ten minutes
from here...
Our mom was going
to come pick us up,
but there must
have been a delay.
[COLLEGE GUY 1] Hey...
where are you headed?
Waiting, huh?
For who?
Us, obviously...
what d'ya say, ladies?
Yeah, I'm sorry...
but we've already
got plans.
We'll show you a good time.
Yeah, it'll be fun.
[MANATSU] You'll be
here in five minutes?
Are you sure?
Eh...?!
What was that...?
I can't hear!
[MANATSU] Sure...
got it.
We'll be here waiting for you.
Standing here
picking up guys, huh?
Nice priorities.
[MAYURA] Shut up.
Earlier you said that
Tabi's more important than
the student council
camping trip.
Tabi is important.
Uh...
sorry...
But what's a Tabi?
He's the very first
horse we ever had!
[IZUMIKO] Horse...?
Your horse...
Here, see.
The area riding club is
looking after him for us now.
He's an old gent these days...
Masumi and I used to ride him.
He's adorable!
Well, at least somebody
here has some sense.
Oh, hey...!
Do you wanna
meet him?
[IZUMIKO] Sure.
But what's
Togakushi like, anyway?
It's a plateau...
Cool temperatures
and fresh air.
Food's not
bad, either.
[MIYUKI] It's pretty famous
for Shugendou Buddhism:
"becoming one
with the deities"
and for all its ninja villages.
Wait...
Ninja?
Yeah, the
Togakushi Shrine...
Supposedly, our
ancestors were priests.
[IZUMIKO] Oh, really?
So, I had some
connections
with an inn.
[car honks]
[SHIZUE] Sorry!
I'm here!
Wow...
I've always dreamed
of a home like this.
We're having a little
barbeque tonight...
Your dad's friends from
the university are coming.
It should be
pretty lively.
Awesome...!
Red meat!
Red meat...!
That's my brother...
He'd do almost anything
for a bite to eat.
Whoever would have
thought twins would turn out
to be so different
from each other?
Now then, all of you...!
I expect you to help
with the preparations!
[GRAD GUY 1] Manatsu...
how's the new school
been treating you?
[GRAD GUY 2] So
hey what about
your horseback
archery...?
Have you been
practicing?
[MANATSU] You bet!
And Mayura is
more lovely
than ever...
We should start
looking for her
future husband
pretty soon!
[MANATSU] What...?!
You think you
can find someone?
[MAYURA] Hey,
I heard that, Manatsu!
[PROF. SOUDA] Here, Sagara.
Go ahead feel free to have
as much as you'd like.
Oh...
Great...
Thanks.
I have to admit...
Haguro...
I was surprised
to hear that
you'd attended
there.
Oh, have you
been as well, sir?
Well, Togakushi and Haguro
share common ground
through Shugendou, after all.
Anyway...
Why don't you
tell me about...
[MANATSU] Izumiko!
Do you want
some fruit punch?
[IZUMIKO] Sure...
that sounds great, thanks.
[MANATSU] Here!
It looks delicious.
I meant to ask you...
Have you ever heard of the MSF?
Huh?
[IZUMIKO] Is it some
kind of club...?
Maybe one you belong to?
Ha, you gotta
be kidding me...
Me, belong to
Mayura's fan club?
[IZUMIKO] A fan club?
[GRAD GIRL 1] Hey Manatsu!
Seriously,
good joke.
Never thought I'd
hear it from you.
[GRAD GIRL 1] What's
this I hear about you
not having a girlfriend?
[MANATSU] Ugh!
You're gonna bring
that up again?
[GRAD GIRL 1] Oh yeah.
I get it.
The Mayura Souda Fan Club...
M...
S...
and F.
[IZUMIKO] That's strange...
I wonder why Miyuki told me
to ask around about it.
Hojou must be a
remarkable place
for that to happen.
The school does
have a nice sense
of independence from the
rest of the world.
[PROF. SOUDA] I see!
I guess that's not surprising.
You should try
to relax more...
You worry far too much
for a girl your age.
[IZUMIKO] Mayura, Manatsu,
and Miyuki all look like normal
high school students
on the outside.
Hey, Izumiko?
What's wrong...?
You're acting weird.
Oh, no.
I'm fine...!
Really, I feel
nice and fluffy.
Fluffy, huh?
[MAYURA] How much
of that did you have?
Oh my gosh, we put a bunch
of liquor in the syrup!
Crap, that's bad...!
Seriously bad!
Miyuki, you're so
silly, Miyuki.
You're kidding me...
Okay, look, go lay down
for a little while.
[MIYUKI] How do
you sober someone up?
Coffee, maybe?
She wouldn't take over
my body, would she?
That wouldn't be fair.
Not when I feel so lovely.
Man, this is so not good!
Wow, that was
a big fall...!
Are you okay?
Mayura's in bed already?
What time is it now...?
I wonder if Manatsu and
Mikyuki are still awake.
Looks like everyone
else is tired too.
[MASUMI] You're
going the wrong way.
Here...
I'm over here.
[IZUMIKO] Oh...
it's him!
Hello there, Masumi!
Hey, you're Suzuhara...
Is that right?
It's so nice that
you remembered me.
But, uh...
what are you
doing out here?
I certainly wasn't
expecting to see you...
Not here...
even Manatsu and Mayura
couldn't find me right now.
You like to come
home sometimes
when no one else is around?
[MASUMI] No, being home
has nothing to do with it.
Oh...
I see...!
This all must be
part of my dream!
No one told me
you were so funny...
Really, you are.
You know, you're the first
person to ever talk to me
without the other two around.
[IZUMIKO] Really?
I am?
[MASUMI] Hey, Suzuhara...
mind if I flirt with you?
Huh?
We should
go out together...
It could be very nice.
Do you get what
you're saying?
Let's say...
yes.
[IZUMIKO] That makes one
of us, because I don't...
What does that kind of thing
even mean over on this side?
Well, you can
learn at Togakushi.
Let's meet up there.
Sound good?
All that fruit.
If you had just
stopped eating it,
everything would have been fine.
Man, Shinkou
scared the
crap out of me...
He seriously
lost his cool.
Just shut up.
[KISARAGI] Morning!
Hope we didn't keep you waiting.
Oh, no...
We haven't been here long.
[KISARAGI] Good, it looks like
everyone's already here...
Go ahead, Souda...
We're all in your hands
for this part of the trip.
Just leave it up to me...
After all...
I'm the one who
suggested camping here.
[FEMALE TOUR GUIDE] Mount
Togakushi's name originates
from the myth of Amaterasu,
who hid in a cave and blocked
the entrance with a boulder...
When Amenitajikoro no Mikoto
forced the cave open,
he threw the boulder,
and one of its pieces
became this mountain.
The deity celebrated
at Togakushi Shrine is a
great nine-headed dragon...
Since ancient times,
Mt. Hiei and Mt. Kouya have--
[IZUMIKO] It's different
than Tamakura...
But in some ways, it's the same.
They are both sacred mountains.
[KISARAGI] This is nice.
Do you come and stay
at this inn every year?
[MAYURA] No, not necessarily...
There is an equestrian
club in the area that I go
way back with, though.
Interesting that you
should mention clubs.
Isn't the History Society
that you happen to belong
to also on a camping trip...?
Right next door?
What are you up to?
Whoa, I'm not up
to anything...!
What would even
make you think that?
Everyone knows the
History Society is really
just another name for
your stupid fan club...
We also know that you're
trying to win over members
of the Executive Committee...
If you try to take over
the Student Council...
don't expect to be successful.
Where's this
all coming from...?
Look, I would never--
It's not fair...!
I haven't done anything
to deserve that accusation!
What are you trying to say?
That I can't join
the Executive Committee?
Sorry, I don't
think that's
what Reina
meant to imply.
She came off a bit too
strong with her comments...
but this is something we want
to make clear from the start.
The Executive Committee will not
shun anyone wishing to join...
but we are adamant about
remaining neutral...
We will not participate in
any of the games on campus...
Do you know why?
We have a responsibility
as judges.
Huh?
I'm a judge.
I possess the power of a Saniwa.
You're the judges.
[KISARAGI] Don't bother denying
that you created the MSF.
Or that you've been working
very hard to put yourself
in a favorable position.
Takayanagi was working behind
the scenes, as well...
However...
bear in mind the Student Council
isn't easily swayed.
[MAYURA]
I understand...
I'll be careful.
Now then...
this is a great
summer retreat...
I would just hate to ruin the
experience with bickering...
Don't you agree?
[KISARAGI] All right!
We'll begin the meeting
about the fall festival.
The Committee Director,
second year Yoshiki Hayakawa,
is currently attending
baseball camp...
so we'll proceed without him...
As we decided the other day,
the theme will be
the Warring States Era...
[IZUMIKO] What was
all that about...?
The History Society is actually
the Mayura Souda Fan Club...?
why does the student council
have to remain neutral?
[IZUMIKO] And to top it all
off, Mayura and Takayanagi are
in some kind of
power struggle...?
I wonder how many of the other
students know what's going on.
[KISARAGI] ...from that point
on, we should be able to come up
with a solid plan...
And that will be
our schedule.
Now, let's enjoy some
free time before dinner.
[IZUMIKO] Oh, wow.
The meeting's already over...
Yes, okay...
I'd really appreciate it if
you could take care of that.
[IZUMIKO] I was wondering
where you ran off to.
[MAYURA] You found me!
[IZUMIKO] Well, um...
about what Kisiragi
was saying before...
Oh, that again...?
Yeah, that wasn't pleasant.
She totally rained on my parade.
I'm confused, though...
What are you and
Takayanagi fighting over?
I mean...
what does he have
to do with anything?
I feel like a walk...
You should come too,
it'll be fun.
[MAYURA] As you know...
I don't like the
Onmyouji spells he uses...
I don't think we
could ever be friends.
[IZUMIKO] Does it have to
do with your ancestors...
since they were shrine
priests and came from
a Togakushi ninja village?
[MAYURA] Maybe a little...
but that isn't
the whole of it...
Kisaragi offered some
pretty sweet info
in her little lecture to me.
[IZUMIKO] I thought
you were offended
by how sharp Akinokawa was.
[MAYURA] Everything
she said was true.
[IZUMIKO] Even how
the History Society
is the Mayura Souda Fan Club?
[MAYURA] I know people have
been calling it that...
And I'm the one who
allowed it to continue.
But the most important thing I
got out of our exchange was that
the Student Council's Executive
Committee is undeniably neutral.
Really?
Really...
And that's
top-secret info...
even at a gossipy place
like Houjou Academy...
Nobody is supposed
to have any idea
who the judges are.
Top secret...
Hey, Izumiko...
She introduced you
to someone, right...?
Former Student Body
President Hodaka Murakami.
You know about that?!
I imagine Takayanagi
does, as well...
Even so...
I still don't know what
happened between you three.
I'm sorry I never
told you, but...
It's just...
I could never think of a good
way to bring it up, you know?
We were both keeping
secrets, so we're even.
It was really
nothing, though...
Not a big deal.
Kisaragi just invited me
to watch her practice.
I figured it was
something like that...
None of the judges are going
to make themselves obvious...
but still...
those who have the power
to see them, will see them.
Honestly...
I was expecting the
academy to be split in two
by the final round...
the festival...
but now I know that
there is a third area void
of outside influence...
That could change
things considerably.
[IZUMIKO] By "split in two"
do you mean a Mayura faction
and a Takayanagi faction?
[MAYURA] He's the
academy's favorite by far.
Do you know what
some people
actually believe...?
That Houjou Academy
was established
for the sole
purpose of
testing his
strength.
I seriously
doubt that.
They allowed
a shikigami to
become a student...
I hope I don't
sound jealous.
I'd never want to use
the spells that he does.
The reason you chose
to set yourself up
as Takayanagi's
opposition...
It's because of
Masumi, isn't it?
That's right...
it's for him...
Masumi...
and Manatsu too.
What would happen
if you were to win?
You don't even
know that...?
That's incredible...
Didn't they tell
you anything when
you enrolled?
[MAYURA] Well...
since we're here, why don't
we go to the rear shrine?
[IZUMIKO] Sure.
[MAYURA] If I win
the final round,
I'll become a World
Heritage Candidate.
[IZUMIKO] A World
Heritage Candidate?
I imagine the
rewards for that
would be substantial...
Both for me...
and for all the people
who are close to me.
So Sagara really
hasn't ever
discussed this
with you?
No I promise...!
That doesn't
necessarily mean
he doesn't know
about it, though.
That's Sagara...
He doesn't tell
anyone everything...
Not even me.
He's sure not an
easy guy to read...
Not at all.
[phone vibrates]
[MAYURA] Apparently, Manatsu
and Sagara are pretty close by.
[IZUMIKO] Huh...?
Really?
Yep...
That's handy...
Let's go and
find them.
Hold on...
Handy...
how?
I have a question...
How would you feel about
beating out Takayanagi...?
and surpassing the shiki user.
[MIYUKI] Do you mean,
like, grade-wise?
[MAYURA] Grades have
something to do with it.
[MIYUKI] He's
using his shikigami.
That's how he's holding
his place as top student.
[MAYURA] That's right...
And unless you can see
a way past his trick...
there's no changing that...
You can never hope
to beat his grades.
Yeah, well...
I don't really care about
being the top-ranked student.
[MAYURA] Then
why did you join
the Student Council's
Executive Committee?
And for that matter,
why did you invite us?
Don't you see...?
Because the Student
Council is neutral.
So it's not
just about you...
You want to make
everybody else neutral, too.
I don't get it,
why do we have partners
in the first place...?
And here's another question...
Aside from the four of us,
do any of the other students
have partners?
Personally...
I think Takayanagi and
his shikigami are getting
preferential treatment.
And I think it's
about time that stopped.
Basically...
there are those of us who
are allowed partners...
and we're capable of rivaling
him, at least to some degree.
So that's
where I stand.
Now it's time to learn
what you're about, Sagara...
It's simple enough, really.
Are you in or are you out?
[MIYUKI] Haven't you known
that for a while now...?
There's no way I could
stand against you...
not while I'm still
such a newbie at defense.
That's along
the lines of what
I've been thinking, too...
However, my father seems
to think otherwise...
He said there's
a lot to more to you.
And how would he know...?
He and I didn't go
into this crap...
Is this the real reason you
invited us to your house?
No, that wasn't why,
actually...
Though I doubt
you'll believe that now.
[MAYURA] You should know...
I want Izumiko on my side...
She has the power to see
shikigami for what they are.
[hurried footsteps]
So, you see...
before you ever
go up against him...
I want to make it clear
which one of us stands
above the other.
Honestly...
Get it through
your head.
I don't
serve her...
'Kay...?
I just want a
normal life...
You know,
like college,
maybe even
a normal job
someday!
Well, you do sound
pretty sincere...
that's too bad...
I'm sorry...
but I have to take my
father's word over yours.
I want to see
your power, Sagara...
Fully unleashed!
♪
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara
can't defend herself!
[IZUMIKO] That's enough, Mayura!
Please don't do this!