That's better.
It's nice to be back.
[MIYUKI] You sure you should
be up and about already?
I'm fine...
I think a good night's sleep
in my own bed is all I needed.
[MIYUKI] Yeah, I kinda had a
feeling that might be the case.
[IZUMIKO] So, you're
practicing early.
[MIYUKI] I need to
get back to my routine.
[IZUMIKO] Oh...
Uh...
Hey, do you know what?
You might be able to
see the ocean from the top of
the mountain this morning...
Want to look?
[MIYUKI] This is
a nice place, huh?
[IZUMIKO] I'm just glad
you got a chance to see it
before you left.
[MIYUKI] Before I left?
[IZUMIKO] Well, I mean, Sagara
changed his mind, didn't he...?
I figured you'd be transferring
back to your old school.
You must be glad.
[MIYUKI] No...
I doubt I could go back there.
[IZUMIKO] What?
[MIYUKI] Well...
I guess you could say I don't
miss it enough to go back.
I've never been able
to figure Yukimasa out...
but I think this whole situation
has cleared some things up
for me.
So tell me something...
Do you remember what
happened back in Tokyo...
with the Hime-gami and all?
Do I remember...?
Well, yes.
Except...
it doesn't feel like
it was me, you know...
It almost felt like
I was just a bystander...
I was there, but someone else
was doing all the talking.
[MIYUKI] That's more
than I expected...
It's actually pretty common
for people not to remember
what happens while
they're possessed.
[IZUMIKO] Wait, possessed?
[MIYUKI] That's what
it's called when a spirit
takes over your body.
He knows her...
Yukimasa knows that spirit.
The Hime-gami that
possessed you...
that's exactly what
he's been searching for.
[IZUMIKO] It's her he's
interested in protecting...
I'm not the one
he thinks is special.
[MIYUKI] It's probably best
if you try to think of her
as a different person.
Fine, all right, then...
Maybe I'm not the one
Yukimasa cares about...
So now can you please stop
giving me such a hard time
and saying that
I'm weak and useless?
This isn't something
to laugh about.
[MIYUKI] Yes...
of course, you're right.
You don't need to worry
about that anymore...
Me teasing you...
I'll be transferring
to Tokyo soon.
[IZUMIKO] Tokyo?
[MIYUKI] Yeah.
That's where
Houjou Academy is...
It's the school Yukimasa
originally wanted to send me to.
I suspect there's something
about the school that may
benefit the Mountain Monks.
[IZUMIKO] Houjou Academy...
Father actually recommended
it to me, as well.
[MIYUKI] I'm not going to avoid
standing in the same ring
as Yukimasa anymore.
Someday I want to possess
the power of a Mountain Monk
in my own right.
[IZUMIKO] I wanted to attend
Sototsugawa High badly enough
to go against Father's wishes...
but now I don't remember why.
[AYUMI] She's here...!
Hey, Izumiko...!
You feeling better?
[IZUMIKO] Yeah.
[HARUNA] So listen...
there's something
we want to ask you.
[AYUMI] It actually
has to do with Wamiya.
[IZUMIKO] Oh...
Okay.
Sure.
[AYUMI] Well, to be honest,
he's a pretty quiet guy,
so it's easy for us to forget
about him sometimes...
We kind of feel bad about
ignoring him, so...
[MATSUBARA] Here!
[HARUNA] Do us a favor...
Give this souvenir to him
on everyone's behalf.
[AYUMI] It should be you.
After all, you were the first
one who noticed he wasn't there
on the field trip.
[HARUNA] Oh, and don't worry...
None of us are going
to fight you for him.
[IZUMIKO] What do you mean...?
Why would I want
to fight with you...?
[AYUMI] Oh, come on, get up your
courage and give it to him...
You can't fool us, we could
tell how sad you were that
he didn't come on the trip
with the rest of the class.
[IZUMIKO] Oh, um...
Hey, Wamiya!
For you...
It's from the girls.
Really...?
Wait, are you sure it's for me?
Yes. I hope
you'll accept it.
[IZUMIKO] It's a shame you
couldn't come on the field trip
with the rest of us, huh?
[WAMIYA] Yeah...
What about you?
Are you glad you went?
[IZUMIKO] Some parts of it
were difficult for me...
but still...
there were some other parts that
made going totally worth it.
[WAMIYA] Well...
I wish you hadn't gone.
[IZUMIKO] What?
[WAMIYA] That
city is corrupt...
tainted...
You shouldn't
have gone there...
You seem like a completely
different person
than before
you went.
Really?
I do?
You aren't planning to
leave this town, are you...?
I want you to tell me you don't
intend to go back to Tokyo.
[IZUMIKO] Why are you
saying stuff like that?
I'd like to
remind you...
It wasn't very long that ago
you told me you hated Sagara.
Well, I did then...
but now...
Now you've had
a change in heart.
If he is responsible
for what you've become...
I will have no choice
but to get rid of him.
[MIYUKI] Come on.
What's gotten into you guys?
[YOHEI] We decided we've
put up with you too damn long
and we're sick of it.
[TOMOYA] Yeah,
you've got a big, fat ego.
I thought I'd been
toning it down.
How embarrassing.
It's about time for us
to kick your sorry ass
outta this school...
Wamiya tells us you've
worn out your welcome.
Wamiya?
Never heard of the guy.
Shut your mouth!
[MIYUKI is punched]
All right...
Just remember,
you threw the first punch~
So what, is this Wamiya
guy behind all of this...?
Where is he?
Lemme talk to him!
You're crazy.
[KAZUTO] We told you to leave.
[WAMIYA throu KAZUTO] You're
nothing more than scum...
And scum doesn't belong here.
[NONOMURA] Purify the
six roots of perception,
cleansing the heart
of all that taints it.
Are you all right...?
Any wounds?
Oh, no, Miyuki!
[MIYUKI] It's nothing serious.
[NONOMURA] It was
just as Izumiko said.
[IZUMIKO] You got into
a fight with Wamiya?
Who's this
Wamiya guy, anyway?
What do you mean,
who is he?
He's Wamiya...
Satoru Wamiya,
a classmate of ours.
Well, I've never
heard of the kid.
What are you
talking about?
[MIYUKI] Roll call
every morning...
Since I'm a transfer student,
my name comes at the very end,
after all the W's
have been called.
There aren't any
students named Wamiya.
[IZUMIKO] That's impossible!
[NONOMURA] Izumiko.
How did you know about this?
What made you think something
bad was going to happen
to Miyuki?
[IZUMIKO] I spoke to Wamiya,
and he didn't seem like
his usual self.
[IZUMIKO] He was saying
something about...
well...
getting rid of you, Miyuki.
Really?
Why?
Well, it's um...
it's difficult
to explain, but...
a while ago I sort of told
Wamiya that I hated you.
And why would you
tell him that?
Because at the
time you were
being really
mean to me!
Make sure
you're buckled in.
I have to floor it.
Something is coming after us.
And it isn't human.
What is it?
Is something
out there?
Wait, you mean you
really can't see it?
[MIYUKI] No...
It just feels like
something's...
off...
You, Nonomura?
[NONOMURA] I see spiritual
energy converging...
It may be a divine spirit.
I think that
classmate of yours
is no mere boy.
He seems to possess the power
to control the other students.
[IZUMIKO] Okay, then...
what does he want from us?
[NONOMURA] If he is
a divine spirit...
They are known to curse
as well as bless.
As to 'why'...
It can be impossible for
a human to know what
will incur their wrath.
Now you've had a
change of heart.
There's more
to all this than
we thought
at first...
It isn't just
you he's mad at.
He's angry with me...
and it's because
of me that he's
directed that
anger toward you.
Could you be
a bit more specific?
It's because
I went to Tokyo.
What, for the fieldtrip?
[NONOMURA] I don't think I can
lose him, but I should be able
to get us to the
shrine, at least.
We must try to make it inside...
The divine protection the
shrine bestows may give us
a fighting chance.
[metal crashing against metal]
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara...
you still alive?
Are you hurt...?
Did you break anything?
[IZUMIKO] I'm pretty sore,
but I'll survive.
[NONOMURA] No serious
injuries, that's good.
I want both of you to get
out of the car carefully.
Look out for
gasoline leaks.
[IZUMIKO] Nonomura?
Y-You're bleeding!
[NONOMURA] I'll be fine.
But it does look like it will
take a while for me to get out.
What do I do?!
[NONOMURA] Above all,
you must not lose heart.
This is the way of things.
Everyone close to the Hime-gami
is expected to risk their lives
to protect her...
Miyuki...
that goes for you, as well.
Tengu mountain deities
can be both protective
and destructive.
[WAMIYA] Speculating about
my nature now, are we?
[MIYUKI]
You're Wamiya.
Is that right?
[WAMIYA] So you can
finally see me, then...
What do I look like?
Nothing special...
Just like a normal
middle schooler.
That's because I am
a normal middle school boy.
Well, at any rate...
That's what I am for as long
as Suzuhara wants me to be.
[IZUMIKO] I don't understand...
It's so strange.
I was convinced I'd
known you for years--
ever since elementary school.
[WAMIYA] I've always been
with you in some way...
Throughout elementary school...
and before.
Think carefully...
When did you first
begin to see me...?
It was right after you cut
your bangs, wasn't it?
I've existed on this
mountain since ancient times.
Parts of me were drifting
about, devoid of form.
Until they converged
around Suzuhara's wish,
creating the shape you see now.
I made a wish...?
I don't remember.
You wished desperately
for a friend, didn't you...?
Somebody who would
truly understand you.
I refuse to let you
pretend otherwise.
After all, it was that
wish that gave me substance.
And I won't let you say
you no longer need me, either.
[NONOMURA] Miyuki...
Get my staff...
It's in the trunk of the car.
You must use it!
I can't...
I don't know how.
[NONOMURA] This
spirit is dangerous.
He possesses true power...
He could kill all of us!
Do you actually think
you'll be able to exorcise me?
[WAMIYA] This mountain
forest is my sanctuary.
[NONOMURA] Hurry, Miyuki...!
Get the staff!
I can't...
I'm not that far along
in my training, yet!
This isn't the time
for self-doubt...
Accept the situation.
You have no choice.
But I do accept it...
That's why I'm so sure...
I can't do this!
[WAMIYA] You are going
to remain here and attend
Sototsugawa High School with me.
From now on, everybody
will treat you kindly...
I'll see to that.
Well, but...
what if I told you that
I'd changed my mind...?
What would
happen to us then?
[WAMIYA] I'm afraid that
is not one of your options.
If you say that you
intend to abandon me...
I'll simply bring a bolt of
lightning crashing down upon us.
[MIYUKI] Wouldn't doing
that defeat your purpose...?
I thought you wanted
to help Suzuhara...
not hurt her.
[WAMIYA] She must pay the
price for using my power.
[MIYUKI] Suzuhara...
Just...
make him happy.
Are you telling me to give in
to the spirit's demands?
That's the only way
out of this...!
You heard
what he said.
He's gonna kill us
if you don't...!
Remember, he's the divine
spirit of the mountain!
[IZUMIKO] How could you
say something like that?!
What happened to
the Miyuki I used to know?
[MIYUKI] But-
Quit thinking about
yourself for once...!
How can you be so selfish?!
If you were truly made from my
wish, then bow to my will...!
Never threaten me
like this again!
Do you understand, Wamiya?
Leave us alone!
[WAMIYA] And if I refuse...?
What then?
Then I will grow
to despise you...
Imagine what
that will be like...
I won't ever come to visit
this mountain anymore...
Is that really what you want?
[WAMIYA] What does it matter
if you despise me or not...?
You are going to be leaving
the mountain in any case.
That may be so...
but wouldn't it be better if
we parted ways as friends...?
Just think about it
and you'll see.
[MIYUKI] Hey...
Suzuhara!
[IZUMIKO] I'll be fine...
I'm just relieved, that's all.
[NONOMURA] If I had
to guess, I'd say Wamiya
was probably a familiar.
[MIYUKI] What do you mean?
[NONOMURA] The
Hime-gami's familiar.
A divine servant who
serves a divine master.
While Izumiko
was still unaware
of their relationship, the
spirit's powers began to run
out of control, becoming
obsessive and dangerous.
But she locked him into the true
master-servant relationship
just in time.
You were magnificent!
[IZUMIKO] In other words...
I was both Wamiya's creator
and his destroyer, wasn't I?
There is no need
to mourn his loss...
It isn't as though Wamiya
no longer exists...
He is probably waiting to form
a new relationship with you.
[MIYUKI] When did you decide you
wanted to go to Houjou Academy?
[IZUMIKO] I didn't know I had
made up my mind until Wamiya
brought it up.
He realized it before
I did and he told me
not to go...
I guess that's why...
Wait, hold on a second.
Let me see if
I've got this straight...
Nonomura and I nearly
got killed...
because you changed your mind
about what school you liked?
He was going to
kill me, too,
so I would say
that makes us
about even...
and don't forget,
Miyuki, I was the
one who stopped
him in the end.
[MIYUKI] It was
all because of her...
I didn't realize just how
dangerous the Hime-gami was.
Anyway...
Seems like I've got
a lot of work to do...
I'm gonna train hard...
so her little pet can't
get the best of me again.
So does that mean
you've decided to
become a Mountain
Monk, after all?
I'm gonna
try to, anyway...
I'm betting
Houjou Academy
is a great
place to start.
I know you're nervous,
but I think it'll be a good
fit for you, too.
Look, I'll transfer
in ahead of you...
and that way I can
tell you what it's like.
Thank you...
I really appreciate that.
[WAMIYA] Could you do one
thing for me before you go?
I would like for us
to have a proper farewell.
[IZUMIKO] Wha...
what do you mean?
Please release me from
my form as Satoru Wamiya...
I am assuming you don't
need him with you anymore.
Yes, of course, but...
how am I supposed
to do that?
[WAMIYA] Think about it...
Don't you often dance on the top
of the mountain by yourself...?
The dance that bound me should
also be able to release me.
It was my dance?
Wait, do you mean...
you mean you bound him
without even knowing
what you were doing?
Yeah, I guess so...
I do dance sometimes, but it's
just supposed to be a workout.
Some workout...
Well, I guess I can't see any
reason for him to lie to us.
Your dancing actually
controlled the divine spirit
of the mountain.
[WAMIYA] That's right.
Now, will you please do me
the honor of releasing me
by performing a dance?
[MIYUKI] Uh...
why are you wearing that?
[IZUMIKO] I guess I didn't
really have to change...
but it's easier to dance when
I have the right sleeves.
And it's okay...?
you don't mind if
I stay and watch?
[IZUMIKO] Of course, I can't
think of what difference
it will make if I show
two people instead of one.
[IZUMIKO] Now that
I think about it...
I really was yearning to have
somebody in my life who could
understand me as I do myself.
Wamiya knew.
And that's why he came to me.
I'm afraid
of being seen...
because I'm afraid
of getting hurt...
I'm embarrassed of being seen...
because...
I'm embarrassed of myself.
I want to change...
I don't want to be this
Izumiko all my life.
I want to change.
[singing in Japanese]
Who is this girl?
And how have I never
seen her before?
[WAMIYA] I suppose I've
been defeated, after all.
She is allowing
somebody else to witness
her dance.
[MIYUKI] You mean you
hadn't actually given up...?
Don't you think
you're being a sore loser?
[WAMIYA] No, as a matter
of fact, I don't think so.
[singing stops]
♪
Welcome to Houjou Academy!
This is a pleasant
surprise, huh?
There's more greenery
than we thought...
Almost like home!
[DAISEI] I told you I would
never encourage you to go
to a school you wouldn't like.
Now do you believe me?
[DAISEI] Hey...!
I haven't seen you in ages...!
Six months now...?
No, it must be longer!
It's nice to
see you again, sir...
It has been a long time...
My father asked me to send his
regrets that he wasn't able
to be here, too.
Is Tokyo as bad
as you remember it?
Are you still afraid of
anything and everything?
[IZUMIKO] I wouldn't say that...
I was fine
coming here this time.
Oh yeah...?
Well, that's certainly
good to hear.
I'm glad.
[MIYUKI] When the new
trimester starts up...
don't tell anybody
about your hometown...
or your powers.
[IZUMIKO] I hadn't planned on
it, but why do you say that?
[MIYUKI] You didn't have to take
the entrance exam, right...?
From what I understand,
there aren't very many people
who are excused from taking it.
Okay...
so why was I exempted, then?
Just think about
it for a second.
[MIYUKI] Houjou Academy
is no ordinary school...
If it was...
why would both Daisei and
Yukimasa be so interested in it?
Hello?
[GIRL] Hey...!
Are you Suzuhara?
My name's Mayura Souda.
You're so cute...! I mean it!
You are just adorable!
I had no idea I would
get such a cute roommate!
I'm so lucky!
[IZUMIKO] I, uh...
[IZUMIKO] Oh, Miyuki, I didn't
realize you knew Mayura.