♪
Isn't the food good?
Yeah!
[annoyed groan]
[MAYURA] I told him to be
here by a quarter 'til.
[MAYURA stands up]
Fine, come on.
We'll just eat without him.
[IZUMIKO] Huh?
Should we be eating here,
since we're technically
middle schoolers...?
I mean...
Isn't this cafeteria reserved
for high school students?
Oh, we'll be fine.
I've actually eaten here
a lot as a middle schooler.
I'd come and say hi to somebody
in the History Society,
which is a high school club,
and we'd end up eating together.
No big deal.
That's so cool.
[BOY] Sorry!
I'm here, I'm here!
[MAYURA] You're
here late, Manatsu.
We haven't even had the
entrance ceremony yet.
Don't tell me you're already
sneaking into the stables.
Guilty!
Did you at least
shower first?
I won't introduce you if
you're covered in horse grime.
I showered.
If I hadn't, I wouldn't
have been late...
Man, I'm freaking starving!
I'm so sorry, Izumiko.
Could we go ahead
and let him eat...?
I'd love to punish him,
but he won't be able to hold
a decent conversation
without fuel.
[IZUMIKO] So you went
here for middle school,
but Manatsu didn't?
He's moving down from
Nagano to serve as
my partner
this year.
He enrolled,
just like that?
With me already
here, he was
exempted from
the entrance exam.
He loves horses, so
he stayed out in the country
through middle school...
And then, big surprise,
the second he got here he joined
the Horseback Riding Club...
I fear for what
the future holds.
[MAYURA]
That's all for you...?!
More physical activity
means more food.
It's not fair you
can eat that much
without getting fat.
Take up horseback
riding...
Bye-bye fat!
Thanks, but I'll
have to pass.
I'm not about to try competing
with you in your specialty.
Hey, your name is
Suzuhara, right...?
Oh, you sure are a quiet one...
Aren't you?
Whose fault
is that?
I'm sorry,
I'm being rude...
My name is Manatsu Souda...
My mounted archery teacher
lives pretty close to here,
so I finally decided
to make the move...
I love horses...
and I hate studying.
Hi, I'm Izumiko Suzuhara...
I, um...
don't have any special
talents to speak of.
[MANATSU] Really...?
I would have thought otherwise.
[IZUMIKO] No...
I'm just bad at a
whole bunch of stuff.
Well, that's great, then.
It means you're
nice and rounded!
That sounds like
sexual harassment.
Right, my bad...
Is it okay if
I get seconds?
Do whatever you want.
I'm telling you,
he's impossible...
And he's always like this.
At first I didn't really
see the resemblance, but
the more I look at you both the
more I can tell you're twins.
The thing is,
we're not twins.
[IZUMIKO] Huh?
Manatsu and I are
actually triplets...
My older brother passed away
when we were really little.
Now it's just us two.
[IZUMIKO] I think I'm
going to get along well
with both of them...
I'm so glad I got
a good roommate.
[MIYUKI] Yeah, I figured you
would get along with Souda.
Oh, Miyuki, I
didn't realize
you knew Mayura.
[MIYUKI] Don't call
me Miyuki here...!
That's what my
stupid father calls me.
I don't like it.
Right, I'm sorry...
Mi--
I mean, Sagara...
So... um...
Yeah, of course I know her...
I mean, how could I not...?
Her grades are even
better than mine.
Probably wouldn't
hurt to let her check
your homework sometimes.
If she's better than you,
does that mean...
she's at the top of the class?
No, he's at the top.
I do hope I'm not
interrupting...
We haven't met.
I thought I should
introduce myself.
Seems you
already know Sagara.
Are you related or something?
This is Izumiko
Suzuhara.
Our parents know
each other...
And this is Takayanagi,
he's a fellow first year.
[TAKAYANAGI]
Hmm...
You have
exceptionally long hair.
Well...
I hope your term gets
off to a good start.
Do you think he--
[MIYUKI]
Resembles Wamiya...?
Yeah, I do...
Except this guy's
actually human.
There's something about him...
something I can't stand.
You decided to
wear your hair down?
Yeah, I'm changing my look!
Think it's weird?
I think you look like
a proper young lady.
[MAYURA chuckles]
[MAYURA] You can't change
your personality as easily
as you can change your hair.
Maybe I'll stop
wearing glasses.
[MAYURA] And what
switch to contacts?
[IZUMIKO] It's not like
I'm blind without them...
I mainly wear them because
they're a gift from my mother.
You've been wearing
non-prescription lenses
this whole time?
No...
I have astigmatism,
and I'm farsighted.
[MAYURA] Oh, yeah...?
Well, either way its like
I've told you before,
I already think
you're adorable.
But you might
be cuter this way.
High school's the
perfect time in life for
a major turning point, isn't it?
Well, let's go!
Oh... sure.
I guess we
won't be together.
It looks like
I'm in Class A...
Oh...!
But, hey, look at that!
You'll be with Manatsu...
Class C.
How'd they divide us...?
By academic aptitude?
We are in different classes,
but Houjou is pretty
flexible about letting
students intermingle.
We can take electives together.
I don't know.
We'll work something out later.
[IZUMIKO] Okay.
[MANATSU] Hey!
Class A, huh?
You must be glad...
If we were together,
the real you might slip out.
And what's wrong
with that?
Izumiko, could you make sure my
dear brother doesn't come off
as too much of a jerk in class?
Uh... 'kay.
[MANATSU] Whoa!
Hey, you're not wearing
glasses like before...!
That's a really
good look for you.
[MAYURA] What about me?
I changed my hairstyle!
[MANATSU] Oh, yeah...
I didn't notice.
You're still the same on
the inside, though, huh?
[MAYURA] What is that
supposed to mean?
[MALE TEACHER] Filling in
for the Student Body President,
Ichijou Takayanagi will
present a welcoming speech
on behalf of the first years.
[BOY 1] He was the top
student for all three years
in middle school.
[BOY 2] Supposedly he comes
from a really rich family.
[GIRL 1] I heard
he's planning on running
for Student Council this year.
[TAKAYANAGI] Hello, and a warm
welcome to Houjou Academy.
All one hundred and three of
us begin this new school year
filled with dreams,
hope, and excitement.
We are lucky to be
learning here in such a rich,
beautiful environment.
With a solid curriculum...
[IZUMIKO] Oh, no!
I thought I was over this.
Am I just upset because
we're in different classes?
I'm not afraid.
I'm not afraid!
[MANATSU]
This is it: Class C!
[MANATSU] Those are
exchange students.
They're from places
like England and Korea...
This school's got
people from all over.
[IZUMIKO] I'm glad
Manatsu's in my class.
[MANATSU] Suzuhara?
Whoa...
You getting sick?
Th-The guy sitting in
the back near the hall...
[MANATSU]
Oh... Ricardo?
He's an exchange
student from Brazil.
Oh, I see.
[MANATSU] What?
Did he do something?
It's nothing.
[YUKARIKO] Wear these.
They'll protect you...
Your eyes are like mine...
They see too well.
[IZUMIKO]
Could that be why...?
The weird thing about horses
is they're all
big scaredy-cats.
Even the littlest
noise or movement
can spook them...
even though they're
not in any real danger.
No offense, but you're kinda
like a horse sometimes.
[IZUMIKO] I can't tell
anyone I'm afraid
of a foreign
exchange student...!
How can I be so preju--
Another one.
It's okay.
Just look again.
[gasps]
Oh, I'm sorry...!
I didn't mean
to scare you.
No, you're fine.
Don't worry.
We were just
wondering...
Have you heard
of Modoribashi?
You mean, like,
the famous bridge?
[TAKASE] No, she
means the website.
Pretty much everybody who's
in Class C knows about it.
Not me...
I don't really
use the internet.
[TAKASE]
All right!
We've got a newbie!
[IZUMIKO]
What's the site for?
[HASEGAWA] It's
like a horoscope...
or an advice site...
Basically, as you go
through it, you get
these inspirational messages.
[TAKASE] The messages
are totally awesome!
I know you're gonna get hooked!
[HASEGAWA] Supposedly Ichijou
Takayanagi from Class A
made the site.
But there is one catch:
you can't get in
without a password.
So do you want it?
[IZUMIKO] I'm sure I'm freaking
myself out for no reason.
Oh my gosh.
[IZUMIKO]
It's not human!
[RICARDO] Excuse me...
Will you come to the media room
after school today?
[IZUMIKO whimpers]
[RICARDO] Well...
will you?
[IZUMIKO whimpers]
[IZUMIKO running]
[RICARDO]
Well... will you?
[IZUMIKO] Fine...!
I'll come, all right...?
Just get away from me!
[IZUMIKO] Sagara, quick!
[STUDENTS gasp]
What are you doing here?
Is it urgent?
Fine, follow me, then.
[MIYUKI] You're afraid of a
foreign exchange student, huh?
[IZUMIKO] I'm not used
to seeing foreigners...
But none of the others scare me.
I was starting to think
every guy freaked you out,
regardless of
where he comes from.
You can't think of any
reason he'd want to see you
after school...?
Maybe you said something...
encouraging?
[IZUMIKO] You don't believe what
I'm saying about him, do you?
You think it's all
a big misunderstanding.
[MIYUKI] No, that isn't true.
I saw Wamiya last year,
remember...?
So I'm not just going to dismiss
your concerns out of hand.
He said to meet him
in the media room?
[IZUMIKO]
Yes, but... I can't go.
[MIYUKI] Try to relax and
I'll figure something out.
Something that
doesn't involve me going?
[MIYUKI] It isn't wise to
break a promise where people
like this are concerned.
But if you're
certain he isn't human,
there are a few ways
we can handle this.
[sighs]
[MIYUKI] By the way...
Did you ditch your glasses?
[IZUMIKO]
Oh, yeah...
[IZUMIKO gasps]
There you are.
Thank you for coming.
[IZUMIKO] That's weird...
He looks normal now.
I have a question for you.
I would like to know
if you are human?
[TAKAYANAGI]
Do my bidding...!
Evil be gone!
[IZUMIKO yells]
Hey...! What was that for?
[TAKAYANAGI]
It didn't work...
You truly are a human, then.
But you're just so
oddly forgettable...
And those pigtails of yours...
Well, no matter.
You are going to
tell me how you saw
through Ricardo's disguise.
[MIYUKI] This is starting
to look a lot like bullying.
That can't be good for
somebody who's running
for Student Council.
[TAKAYANAGI] Ricardo and
I have done nothing wrong...
You're the one who
would get in trouble.
Bringing a weapon to school...
[MIYUKI] Except I don't have
a single arrow with me.
[TAKAYANAGI] Heh. Then why
did you even bring it?
[MIYUKI] Lend my weapon
strength and wisdom...
Pierce the heart of evil
and dispel falsehood,
bringing light.
Let it turn
danger into safety.
I'm glad he's gone,
but what was he...?
I mean, is it okay
that we got rid of him?
I allowed him to
be dispelled...
There are better ways I could
have handled that, I suppose.
You gave yourselves away
by revealing that the girl
was a human...
So you're a medium,
aren't you...?
And your partner is an ascetic.
Yeah, so what?
You can only use
living people
to do your bidding, which
makes you a waste of my time.
When it comes to skill...
I'm in a different class.
Hey, hold still...
You've got something
on your back.
Well, what is it?
A talisman...
I think.
[MAYURA] Yeah, obviously.
You should have been able
to figure that out at least.
[MIYUKI] Souda?
How long have you been
standing back there?
Don't worry.
I was going to step in
and help if things
started to turn ugly...
But I didn't want Takayanagi
to know I was here
if there was any way around it.
[MAYURA] You're amazing,
you know that?
You must be the
first person ever
to recognize his shikigami--
his familiar...
Now I know that he's an
Onmyouji Shikigami User,
and it's all thanks to you.
Sorry, what's
an Onmyouji?
[MAYURA]
He's a type of priest.
So what, are you
an Onmyouji too?
[MAYURA]
No! Of course not.
Well I'm not sure...
It explains why you know
so much about them...
as well as why you were
hiding and watching all this.
Wow. You really don't
understand how this school
works yet, do you?
For starters, no one here
would ask a question like that
to another student's face...
Although, they might fish
around behind your back...
I knew there was something
about this academy
that was out of the ordinary.
[MAYURA] Since I have
nothing against you,
I'll answer your question.
My expertise is in a field
not too different from yours
as a Mountain Monk.
Unlike Takayanagi,
I don't have the ability
to control shiki...
But I don't want to, either...
I'm sure it would warp my mind.
[MIYUKI] I'm not sure
it's not already warped...
Anyway...
What do you think
he was trying to do?
Now, this is just me
thinking out loud, of course...
but more and more Takayanagi
seems to care way too much
about being at
the top of the class...
and I don't like it.
It annoys me to no end
that he ranks above me.
Yeah, that guy
pisses me off, too.
At least we agree on
one thing, then, huh?
By the way, Izumiko...
I was wondering.
What was this note for?
[MIYUKI] Why would he set up
something like this?
[MAYURA] He's secretly
winning people over.
The little sneak!
Well...
it is a clever way to
increase supporters.
[MAYURA] Let's see the
site first and then decide
if it's clever.
Protect yourselves!
Cloak me in
protective armor!
[groans]
[MIYUKI]
Are you okay?
[IZUMIKO] Mayura!
[door opens]
[IZUMIKO] You're back!
Are you really okay?
I've been so worried about you!
[MAYURA] Calm down...
I already told you it wasn't
anything to be concerned about.
[IZUMIKO]
I'm so sorry...
It was all my fault.
And how could what somebody
else did be your fault?
Because I'm the one who
told you about that
horrible website
in the first place...
I wish I could take it back.
Takayanagi would've
found a way to target me
sooner or later,
no doubt about it...
Though I didn't expect him
to use a curse that was
life-threatening...
That part was
a rather nasty surprise.
You mean what he did
could have killed you?
Anyway, enough about me.
The curse didn't
touch you, did it?
That's a relief at least.
So, were you the one who
pushed me out of the way?
Well, was it you
or wasn't it?
Well... tell
me something...
Which answer would
make you happier...
That it was me who saved you...
or that it was Sagara?
Please don't tease me.
Heh. I'm being serious...
Do you remember when
Takayanagi called you two
an ascetic and a medium?
Yes, but what does
that even mean?
The medium lets the
ascetic redirect a spirit
into her when he
exorcises someone...
In the Middle Ages,
it was pretty common for
a Mountain Monk and a
priestess to work together
as a married couple.
A married couple?
Maybe it would be
easier if I just asked you
straight out.
Are you two a pair?
No, it's not
like that at all!
Okay, I get it.
I'm willing
to play along.
You're just saying
all this stuff to
mess with me,
aren't you?
[chuckles]
[knock on window]
[MAYURA] Ah! Manatsu?!
[IZUMIKO] Uh...
You do know this is
the girls' dorm, right?
[MANATSU] Yeah...
I know.
Sagara's back from the hospital.
He told me what happened.
[MAYURA]
You spoke to Sagara.
You idiot!
What the hell
were you thinking?!
Please, um...
Could you maybe
lower your voi--
Sticking your neck
out for no reason!
What's so important it was
worth getting hurt for...?
Is this school
just a game to you?!
[MAYURA sobs]
[MAYURA] Manatsu...
you jerk.
Do you know how
scared I was...?
Do you?
It'll be okay.
[IZUMIKO] I've never
leaned on someone.
Not like she's
leaning on him now.
But maybe that's because I've
never pushed myself so far
that I've needed to.
[throat clearing]
[IZUMIKO] What
are you doing?
[MIYUKI] Sorry, I know
my timing really bites
but is it okay
if I come in?
What is it?
Why are you here?
When I got back, he
rushed over and insisted
that I tell him
absolutely everything...
He got me kinda worried, so...
[IZUMIKO]
Are you hurt?
It's nothing
serious, really.
[MAYURA] Aw, jeez...
I can't believe
you saw me like this.
[MANATSU] Listen...
I'm putting an end to this...
tonight...
Are you up to it?
What are you
planning to do?
Takayanagi played
a dirty, dangerous trick...
and he deserves to be punished.
I'm with you.
I approve of
settling the score.
[MAYURA]
Yeah, but...
What's wrong?
Does it hurt so badly that
you can't even summon Masumi?
[MAYURA]
Mm-mm.
That isn't
the problem...
I was just kind of hoping I
would be able to go personally.
[IZUMIKO]
Masumi...?
[MANATSU and MAYURA]
Protect me and purify me...
Guide me and deliver me.
Prepare me for the
divine spirit's coming...
Shelter me now and
give me strength.
He came, didn't he?
He's ready for action.
Stay here
and rest up...
You know you can
always see him later.
Would you go with them?
I'd like you to get a
good look at Masumi...
I want you to see how different
he is from a shikigami.
[MANATSU] Suzuhara...
This is Masumi.
♪
[MIYUKI] I don't care
if you're a judge!
I still don't want
you coercing her!