Hey.
Where the hell're we goin'?
For all I know he's
about to boil me in oil,
or throw me off a cliff.
I've gotta find
a way outta here.
I hate to bother you,
maid lady,
but could I swing by
the bathroom really quickly?
Soon as I'm untied I'm gone.
I wish I could help you
but unfortunately the Master
has ordered me not to let you
out of my sight for any reason.
Feel free to let loose here
and I'll clean it up later.
Don't worry.
You must think I've brought
you here to torture you,
but I assure you
that's not the case.
So make yourself at ease.
What is this place?
The weapons are
arranged on the wall.
The weapons?
You may use
whichever you like best.
Unless you'd prefer
to fight barehanded.
Are you kidding me?
You wanna duel?
How else will we know who is
better qualified to protect Rea?
You and I have a score
to settle, Furuya.
Looks like she's got more
than enough money for cab fare.
Father!
Good afternoon, Mistress.
Welcome home.
Where is he?
I demand to speak to my father!
Sorry but I'm afraid
you can't do that.
Master Dan'ichiro
is busy at the moment
and has asked that
he not be disturbed.
I couldn't care less
if he's busy!
I know he had Chihiro
kidnapped and brought here.
I don't know what
to tell you, Mistress.
I have an idea, why don't you
spend some quality time with us
while you're waiting
for the Master?
[REA yells]
[MAID knocking on door]
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Madam Aria?
Mistress Rea is in
our care once again.
Oh.
Would you like to go see her?
Why should I?
Give me one good reason I should
welcome that little bitch home.
What's going on?
I don't understand.
Why're you doing this?
I apologize for
being so rough with you.
We're simply
following the orders
given to us by the Master.
In that case, I'll give
you an order of my own.
Take these shackles off me now!
Silly girl, don't you know
the household staff only
takes orders from
the Sanka family heir?
It's hard to believe our
demure Mistress could turn into
such a pushy young lady
practically overnight!
[MAIDS laughing]
Yeah, I think I liked
her better the other way.
I don't see why we can't
knock some sense into her
as long as Master Dan'ichiro
never finds out about it.
You're right.
What he doesn't
know won't hurt him
and we may never
get the chance again.
Wait.
What're you going to do to me?
No!
That's the cutest thing ever!
Hey! I'm not some kind of doll
for you to play
dress up with, you know!
We've always wanted to see
what you'd look like in one
of our uniforms, Mistress Rea!
And you look just as cute
as we thought you would!
You cowards!
Why would you
pull a stunt like this
when I can't
even defend myself?
How could you be so cruel?
Aw, she looks even cuter
when she's angry, doesn't she?
What should we
dress her up as next?
A ninja?
A stuffed animal?
Geez.
I so don't have time
for this right now.
I've got a bad feeling.
I hope he's okay!
Chihiro!
Is something wrong?
I thought I made myself clear.
All you have to do
is strike me once,
and you will be
declared the victor.
It still doesn't seem fair.
I don't know the last thing
about fencing and you're a pro.
I never said you had to fence.
You may use
whatever fighting style
you feel most
comfortable with.
I'm not comfortable
with any of them.
I'm not a fighter!
What kind of a man goes through
life without ever learning
how to defend himself and
protect those he cares about?
Do you honestly believe
Rea would be foolish enough
to run off with
a coward like you
when she has a valiant
protector in me?
You mean you really don't
know how she feels about you?
I know somethin' you don't know,
and I'm not gonna tell you!
[CHIHIRO laughing]
I don't know if I can
take much more of this!
Her hyper-cuteness
is killing me!
Okay, you've had your fun.
Now would you let me go?
As we told you before,
we're not allowed to take orders
from anyone
but the Sanka family heir.
I guess you're stuck here.
Can we put her in
the ninja outfit next?
Okay, as long as we can
do the stuffed animal
costume after that.
Maybe.
Let's wait and see what happens.
I thought we were
gonna take turns?
Let's just play it by ear.
Don't get your panties
in a bunch.
I'm not wearing either of them.
I'm sorry, but I don't
have the time for this!
This guy's painfully
out of touch, isn't he?
Excuse me?
Care to elaborate?
There's not much more
to say except.
You are a poophead.
"Poophead"?
I'm just callin' it
like I see it, pops.
Deciding Rea's
future with a duel
instead of taking her feelings
into account is
totally uncool in my book.
It takes a special kind
of self-righteous jerk
to kidnap a guy just
to get his point across.
You must be
pretty desperate, huh?
And don't even get me
started on the whole
taking nude pics of your
daughter on her birthday thing.
How in the hell do
you know about that?
I've heard of some
twisted things in my time,
but your obsession
with Rea takes the cake.
Can you really
blame her for wanting
to get as far away
from a creepy, old man
like you as she possibly can?
Chihiro!
In all seriousness,
this isn't our decision to make.
We could duel until
we're blue in the face
and it wouldn't change anything.
In the end, all that
matters is what Rea wants.
She's almost an adult
so she doesn't need anyone,
especially not her
overprotective father,
making decisions for her.
It's her life
so let her live it.
You know, I think I've
finally got you figured out.
You say you
want to protect Rea
but what you really
want is to control her.
You know that's
not normal, right?
I gotta say, I was more
than a little creeped out
when Aria told me your obsession
with her seemed to stem
from the fact that you couldn't
let go of the love you
felt for her mother.
So why don't you--
Sorry to interrupt.
I simply couldn't take any
more of your incessant chatter.
How dare you accuse
me of indecency?
As the Sanka family heir,
I have the power to erase
your existence entirely.
Isn't that right. Rea?
What have you done?
Whoa.
The Master ran him through!
Shh!
I'm sorry it had
to come to this,
but that's what you get
for not taking me seriously.
Why, you!
In your face.
What the hell do
you think you're doing?
You thought I was
a goner, huh, pops?
Are you okay?
Rea! I'm sorry.
I didn't see you standing there.
Whoa!
What's with that getup?
Talk about a match
made in heaven! Or hell.
Who knew the zombie
bunny girl look
would be way hotter
than the zombie nurse?
Uh, the maids forced me
to wear different costumes.
Who cares about my dumb outfit,
aren't you in pain?
Furuya!
How are you standing
after I've impaled you?
Oh, yeah.
Pretty crazy, huh?
I wish I could tell ya
but I'm not sure myself.
I suppose it could be because
I'm worked up right now
and my adrenaline is racing.
Or maybe...
That's it! Of course!
I must've been infected when
Rea licked my wound at the park.
It seems she
inadvertently infected me
with her poison while
disinfecting one of my wounds.
Oh no!
What did I do to him?
My heart is still
beating normally
so I obviously didn't
receive a lethal dosage.
Apparently, it was just
enough to anesthetize any pain.
And that can only
mean one thing.
I'm now what you'd
call a "half-zombie."
What? A zombie?
Not you, too!
In that case...
I'll cut off your head!
Father, you've
done enough damage.
Now stop.
You've already dealt
the finishing blow
so there's no
need to continue.
You had an unfair
advantage against Chihiro.
If you want to keep fighting
you'll have to take me on.
I don't want to fight you, Rea.
All I have ever wanted
is to save you from
your mysterious affliction.
I'm determined to find a cure
because I want you
to live a long and happy life.
Can't you see that I only
want what's best for you?
I've hired a team
of doctors in America
and I've made arrangements
for us to move there.
If we surround ourselves
with the greatest doctors
and researchers
from around the globe.
They may be able--
No, they will be able
to find a cure for your disease.
I have the money and power
to ensure that you survive.
A boy with limited resources
and a ninth grade education
could never do as
much to save you.
You're right, Father.
The thing is that I don't
really want to be cured.
What do you mean?
This isn't something
we can simply ignore.
This is life or death.
If finding a cure means
that I have to move far away.
I'll take my chances here.
And even if it's only
for a little while,
I'd like to stay
and spend whatever time
that I may still have
left with my best friend.
Rea.
I don't understand. Why?
You would give up
everything you have for
a fleeting taste of freedom?
But you're special.
You're a beloved member
of a dignified family.
Listening to you talk, it's like
you barely know her, Pops!
What'd you call me?
Rea couldn't care less
about being "special"
like the rest of you!
Can you think of
a single time in her life
where you let her
have what she wanted?
Or have you always denied her?
You won't believe
what I found, Father!
I was digging in the gardens
and I found a snail!
Look!
I want you to be
more careful, Rea.
A privileged girl like you
shouldn't play with
such filthy things.
Understand?
If it's okay.
I'd like to go shopping
with my friends.
Or you could stay
home and make a list
of what you want
and I'll buy it for you.
How's that sound?
It's hard to believe Rea's
already in high school.
We'll need to
keep an eye on her.
I don't want any lowlife
cads her age coming near her.
She's spoken for.
She will only be accepting one
set of genes in her lifetime.
What is with you?
Why can't you see?
All she's ever wanted
is to be a normal girl!
How could I be so blind?
It's because of
my controlling ways.
That's why you
died and left me.
I pushed you away from me.
It was my fault.
Now that's out of the way,
I will admit there's
one thing you said about me
that I completely agree with.
I realize I don't have the same
resources that you do,
and I'm well aware there're many
things I can't do on my own.
That's why,
when those things come up
I'd like us to be able
to work together from now on.
I don't wanna lose Rea because
we can't see eye to eye.
Oh. Chihiro.
Tell me.
Are you positive that
you have no regrets, Rea?
Yes, sir.
Very well then, Furuya.
I have decided I shall leave
my daughter in your care.
Are you being serious?
Do you really mean that?
However, this is
a temporary agreement
only to be recognized
while I am overseas
searching for a cure
for Rea's affliction.
I am not ready to hand
her over to you forever.
That sounds fair to me, sir.
One more thing.
Just because
she's in your care
doesn't mean you have the right
to deprive her of her chastity.
Uh. I swear I'd never
do such a thing!
What did he say to you?
Oh, nothing.
Definitely not
what you're thinking.
Don't worry your pretty,
little head about it.
I was worried this
was gonna be the end.
Thank goodness
we worked it out.
Rea and I get to live
together a little longer.
Chihiro!
Are you alright?
Please! Answer me!
No!
Would you care
for a beverage, sir?
No, thank you.
I was so worried about you!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Sorry, that probably hurt, huh?
What the hell?
So much for never
feeling pain again.
Looks like the poison in
my system's been used up
and now I'm back
to normal again.
This totally blows!
Thankfully, Satsuki
and I were here
to stitch you up and nurse
you back to health.
You have miraculously
come back to life, hooray.
How can that be when
I was never even dead?
I can't tell you how
happy I am right now!
It's just you lost so
much blood that for a while
I was worried we were
going to lose you forever.
I hate to think I made you
worry about me like that.
Sorry, Rea.
It's no big deal.
So, what's with
the nurse costume?
Huh? Oh, this?
I wasn't going to wear it,
but the maids convinced me
because they thought
you might like it.
So be honest.
Does it look okay on me?
Heck yeah!
You bet it does!
I love zombie nurses.
Just when I thought he
couldn't get any creepier.
Chihiro!
No, wait, Wanko!
I was so worried
about you, dummy!
Mero called.
She said you'd been hurt,
so I rushed over
as fast as I could!
If you know I'm injured then why
did you jump right on top of me?
Oh, sorry about that.
Now quit givin' me a hard time
and tell me how
this happened to you.
Well, you see--
It was all my fault.
I mean, I'm not
the one who hurt him,
but he got into
a fight because of me.
May I ask why
you're dressed as a nurse?
Because Chihiro
loves zombie nurses.
You've got her wearing
skimpy costumes, you sicko?
I'll have you know
I had nothing to do with it!
But you think it's hot.
Well yeah, of course I do!
That was a dirty trick, Mero!
As much as I hate to admit it,
I'm afraid I'm
the one responsible
for getting Chihiro
into this situation.
That isn't true
and you know it!
What?
You're Rea, right?
Don'tcha think it's weird for
a zombie to live near a temple?
Uh... not really.
Hmm
I'm sorry but I don't think
we've been properly introduced.
I'm Ranko Saoji and I'm one year
ahead of you at Sanka Academy.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Chihiro's older sister
figure and fiancée.
And I'm human!
Are you surprised?
You know she's joking, right?
She's just trying to
get a rise outta you.
Why the hell would you even
say something like that
to her when you know it's a
bold-faced lie, Wanko?
A lie?
Well, that's news to me
'cause you promised
we'd get married back when
we were in grade school.
Chihiro!
Whaddya want now?
When we grow up will
you be my fiancé?
I don't even know
what that means.
Just say you'll do it, dummy!
Yeah, alright, whatever you say.
How'm I supposed
to remember
some stupid thing
I said as a kid?
I was just kidding!
I'm sorry if
I freaked you out, Rea.
I always get a kick
out of watching Chihiro
squirm under pressure.
It's pure comedy!
Hey!
What happened to all the tears
you were cryin' a minute ago?
As if I'd ever cry
over your lame ass.
You're such a liar!
Here's a newsflash for ya,
I was just acting, too!
You ain't winning any
awards for that performance.
Enough!
You'd better tell
me what went down,
or I'll have to noogie you!
I'm not sayin' a word 'til you
let me out of this headlock.
Yeah right,
in your dreams, buddy!
I can tell by
the look in her eyes.
This Ranko girl.
She's in love with him, too.
I knew Mero was frustrated,
but I can't believe
she actually quit.
I can't say I'm surprised.
She may be mature but
she's still a twelve year old.
You ready to do this?
Yeah!
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 12,
"At That Moment... I..."
Tune in to see Mero!
You're back!
Oh, thank goodness!
I'm not running away anymore.