[CHIHIRO] Hey,
are you all right?
[REA] Hmm?
I just noticed that
you're limping.
Oh.
I guess I must've
twisted my ankle
a little when I fell earlier.
But it looks
worse than it is.
I'll be fine.
Geez.
Hey, wait a minute...
just what do you
think you're doing?
Careful!
Watch where you
put your hands!
There.
[CHIHIRO thinking] The whole way
home... it was radio silence.
Neither of us said a word.
I should've used that time
to get to know her better.
If I'd asked her about her
about her hopes and dreams...
maybe she would've opened up
about her problems at home.
Thinking back on it now.
I feel like I dropped the ball.
That walk home
was my last chance
to save her,
and I blew it.
Rea...
How dare you!
How could you
betray me like this?
I don't know that
I'll ever trust you again.
From this day forward,
you are never to
leave the house!
Not even to go to school!
I don't want you
seeing anyone!
You have no need
for friends!
I can't take it anymore.
No one should
have to endure this.
Drinking the potion
is the only way
I can escape
this wretched life.
They will never care
for you as much as I do!
I am the only person you need...
do you understand?
Well... I'm still alive.
Guess I'll have
to face another day.
Good morning
Mother and Father.
It's a beautiful day.
Wouldn't you agree?
Well, you're certainly in
good spirits this morning.
Can't imagine why.
I heard about the stunt
you pulled yesterday.
Sneaking out of the house
and coming back late at night.
What were you thinking?
I can tell you're
disappointed with me, Mother.
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't leave
the house unattended
but the moon was so pretty
I had to take a walk.
Cut the crap.
You're on thin ice,
young lady.
I'm not going to have
my good reputation
sullied by your
promiscuous behavior.
Don't take that
tone with her, Aria.
She's already apologized
for her indiscretion.
Whatever you say, dear.
You're not going to stay
and join us for br--
I'm not hungry.
About last night.
I apologize for
losing my temper.
It was inappropriate of me
to slap you that way.
No, that's not true.
I deserved it.
I know that sneaking out
of the house is dangerous,
but I did it anyway.
I'm lucky to have
made it home safely.
You are lucky, aren't you?
I'm glad you're able to see
things from my point of view.
Just remember...
I do these things
because I care.
No man will ever
love you like I do.
[DAN'ICHIRO...]
I know.
I just noticed your clothes.
May I ask why you're
wearing your school uniform?
I thought I made
myself clear when I said
you would be
homeschooled from now on.
Oh yeah...
You did say that.
I guess it's just habit.
I'm sorry, Father.
I hate to interrupt, sir.
Rea dear.
Why don't you
go change clothes?
Yes, sir.
I'll do that right away.
Did you find out anything?
Indeed, sir.
I have identified
the young man
who was the cause of
last night's "incident."
He's a freshman student
at Shiyo High School
who lives with his family
in a temple off Second Street.
[Dan'ichiro] I see.
[REA thinking] Could they
be talking about Chihiro?
We must ensure he'll never
lay a hand on my daughter.
I want the boy castrated.
[REA gasps]
Why would he
do such a thing?
Chihiro's in danger.
I have to warn him!
[RANKO] Are you insane?
Please tell me
you're joking!
[CHIHIRO] Hey Babu!
Where are ya, little buddy?
[RANKO] You expect me
to believe you whipped up
a reanimation potion,
fed it to your dead cat,
and now he's alive?
If that's true, you're not
setting a very good example
as the son of
a temple priest.
Dummy.
Am I wrong to think this calls
his morality into question?
No, I completely agree.
I've always thought my brother's
morals were questionable
because of his bizarre love
of zombies but I never imagined
he'd go to such lengths
to interact with one.
I just wanted
my cat back, okay Mero?
You got me.
I will admit that attempting
to resurrect the dead
is more than a little creepy.
But who cares
'cause it did the job
and now Babu
is alive and kickin'!
C'mon, why can't you just
say you're happy for me?
You know how much
I missed my little buddy!
Right?
Chihiro, I'm really
starting to worry about you.
I mean, you don't
honestly believe
you brought him
back to life do you...
ecause that's impossible.
How can you say that when
he's right in front of you?
[BABU meows]
Did you hear that?
There's no mistaking
his weird, nasally meow.
I'm telling you, that's him!
There's no doubt about it!
That meow did sound like him,
but there's
something about him
that seems off...
you know?
I don't remember his eyes
glowing that brightly.
And I hate to say it
but he doesn't seem
to be quite as
affectionate as before.
Okay, but other than that
he really hasn't changed, right?
This could get you
in serious trouble.
For what?
I didn't hurt anybody!
Not yet anyway!
I'd think you, of all people,
would be aware of the risk.
What if he starts attacking
people now that he's a zombie?
If his victims
turn into zombies too,
it won't be long 'til we're
outnumbered by the undead.
Aw c'mon, that kinda stuff only
happens in zombie movies.
I wouldn't be so sure
about that if I were you.
Where do you think
you're going, Babu?
Don't let him get away!
You forgot your
backpack, brother.
Don't you need it?
Thanks, Mero,
but I don't think
I'm gonna make it
to school today.
He can be such a weirdo.
Mero! What's going on?
What's with all
the damn ruckus?
Oh, hey there Grandpa.
Brother found another
stray he wants to take in
and instead of just asking Dad,
he's insisting that he's brought
Babu back from the grave.
Well, I'll be!
Babu's back, huh?
And to think your brother's
the one who did it, too.
That's my boy!
What the heck's
gotten into you?
I used to pick you up
all the time,
you never had
a problem with it before.
Be careful.
Don'tcha think you should
be using gloves to catch him?
I can handle this
on my own, Wanko.
I'm sure you don't
wanna miss practice.
Why don'tcha go to school?
As your elder, I feel
obligated to watch over you
so you're not gonna
get rid of me that easily.
You're barely older than me!
Whoa, he just
jumped in that hole!
You're not going
in there, are you?
Wanna share a glass with me?
I hope that little bitch
walks all over you!
It's so freakin' dark in here
I can barely make out
what's right in front of me.
Hey!
Would ya slow down
and lemme catch up?
Ow, this is starting to chafe.
I keep crawling but it feels
like I'm not getting anywhere.
I'm stuck, Chihiro!
I could really
use a hand about now.
Hello?
I realize that Babu's
your priority but come on!
You can't seriously go off on
your own and leave me like this!
I know you can hear me!
Chihiro!
Why are you such an idiot?
I thought it was
never gonna end.
Huh?
That's strange.
How on earth did I end up here?
[WALLA: MALE STUDENTS]
So, Mogi...
do you like baseball?
Yeah. I like
watching it.
And I suppose
you like girls.
Yeah, watching them.
So you're like
a stalker or somethin'.
I thought you
were into dudes
but it turns out
you're just painfully shy!
Stop it!
How's that feel?
You like it, don'tcha?
Coochy-coochy-coochy-coo!
Yeah, that was
outta line, huh?
I'm sorry about
sexually harassing you, Mogi.
I'm just so horny that
I can't control myself.
What's wrong with you?
You were like a madman!
Why did you get
all handsy with me?
Because I can't get my hands on
the girls at Sanka Academy!
[REA] Excuse me.
I hate to interrupt,
but may I ask you something?
Do you know a boy
named Chihiro by any chance?
I kinda need to find him.
Who?
What did you say?
I'm looking for
Chihiro Furuya.
He goes to your school.
He's a friend of mine
and I need to talk to him.
He's... your... friend?
Don't leave the lady hanging!
Have you seen him, Mogi?
Nope, I haven't.
In fact, he usually
walks to school with us
but he was nowhere to
be found this morning.
Oh, goodness.
Well, that worries me.
You know, if you need to talk
to Furuya you can wait here.
I can take care of your other
needs in the meantime.
[YASUTAKA humping fence]
[REA] No... No thanks.
It's just...
Well, he's in danger
of being castrated.
No way.
Did... Did you just
say Furuya's gonna be...
Cas-Cas-?
[REA] Um...
Please just forget
that I said anything, okay?
No! No, don't go!
At least tell me what
the hell you see in that loser?
That was incredibly
nerve-wracking.
I hope I didn't say anything
that might embarrass him.
I can't worry about that now.
I have to find him.
[DAN'ICHIRO] What?
Rea snuck out of
the house again?
No, leave her be for now.
But follow her every move.
Why must you be
so difficult, child?
I don't understand
why you won't obey.
Damn. This sucks.
I'm never gonna
find Babu in here.
I can't believe Wanko ditched
me without even saying a word.
So much for her obligation
to watch over me.
[thunder clap]
Uh-oh, looks like
it's gonna rain.
It's Babu!
Why is he eating
hydrangea leaves?
Hang on.
Isn't this where I found Rea?
Yep, sure enough.
This is the ledge she was
trying to climb up yesterday.
What the--?
What is she doing here
in the middle of the day?
We made plans to meet
at the hotel tonight
for Babu's funeral.
I'll wait for him there.
I just hope I can make it.
I have to warn him.
It's the least I can do.
All of this is my fault.
I never meant to cause
Chihiro any trouble.
[DAN'ICHIRO] How much farther
do you intend to walk Rea?
Sneaking out for a walk
in the woods again?
I don't suppose you'd explain
what possessed you to climb
all the way up here?
Well?
Who's that guy
she's talking to?
If it's her old man,
things could get ugly.
Let's get you home.
I'm willing to overlook
this incident
if you'll promise
to obey me from now on.
You're much too smart
to behave like this.
A delicate flower like you
shouldn't be wandering
the woods alone.
You should stay inside
the house where it's safe.
[REA] No!
I wonder what
they're talking about.
My heart is broken.
How could you disrespect
your father like that, Rea?
What have I done?
You've hurt me.
More than you could ever know.
I know you care,
and that you're just
trying to protect me.
But you don't have
the right to act
as though my body
and soul belong to you.
Just because I'm your daughter,
it doesn't mean you're
allowed to hold me prisoner.
I'm not your property, Father.
I'm a human being,
and I deserve to
have my freedom.
Really?
And precisely
what kind of "freedom"
are we talking about here?
Could you  be more specific?
Answer me, child.
Do you simply
want the "freedom"
to go outside
whenever you please?
Or is there more to it?
Do you desire
the "freedom" of love?
Let go, Father!
Let's talk about this!
If you'll let me stay I promise
I'll never disobey you again!
I know better!
You just want to see
that Furuya boy!
Where in the hell did
that mangy cat come from?
Keep away from us
you putrid animal!
Is that really you, Babu?
I'm warning you!
Stay back!
I'm highly allergic!
Babu!
It is you!
I don't believe it!
He actually brought
you back to life.
Rea! Wait!
Whatever you do,
don't touch that mongrel!
He could contaminate you!
I guess this means
Chihiro perfected
the reanimation potion
last night after I left.
I wish I could've been there.
What if the mixture I drank
was the one that worked?
Stand back, Rea!
No! Don't hurt him, Father!
Please!
No!
Rea!
Chihiro.
Rea, no.
Rea! Answer me!
[CHIHIRO crying]
You weren't supposed
to actually die.
I thought you were
just joking around.
Were you serious?
I want you to bring me
back whenever I die.
I'm sorry but...
I just can't do it.
[REA] Chi...
Chi... hiro.
Chihiro.
Whoa.
No way.
I didn't even give
you the potion but you...
You're alive.
Dear God,
how could this happen?
Master Dan'ichiro, sir?
Chihiro please.
I've asked
you this once before,
but now that I'm a zombie
will you please take care of me?
Rea, I... Uh.
Okay.
Sorry I've been kinda moody
the last few previews
but that won't happen again.
I finally got to meet
with the writers
and I'm happy to say that
everything's been resolved.
I had a nice,
long talk with them.
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 4
"A Normal... Girl."
Tune in to see Mero!
They said they're trying to
appeal to our male fan base.
Apparently, men are suckers
for cutesy crap.