[MERO] Not to state the obvious,
but the Furuya household
is also a temple.
There've been a few minor
changes around here lately.
For starters, we've got
a zombie staying with us,
but I'm sticking
to my routine.
I mean these chores
aren't gonna do themselves.
[CHIHIRO] Hey, Rea!
Don't stay
outside too long.
The sun's awfully
bright today.
I'll be inside in a minute.
Oh, hi, Mero!
Hello?
What's her problem?
Come on, it's way too hot!
[MERO] I'm sure
you're all concerned
about the high-tension
cliffhanger predicament
my brother and Rea have
got themselves into.
But never fear.
I'd like to offer
you a brief respite
from their dreadful drama.
Now enjoy this palate-cleansing
side dish of a story.
Hey, Mero.
It's time for me
to head out for the day.
Do you think you'll
get home late again tonight?
Most likely.
I've got three different
parishioners to visit.
I'll try to eat dinner
before I come home.
Sure, less work for me.
And Chihiro said
he's going out with Rea
so don't bother making
anything for him either.
Well that's unusual.
He's sure surprised me.
I'll admit I was a little
skeptical at first.
Him wanting to take
responsibility for Rea and all?
But here he is,
still sticking to it.
Yeah, it's kind of bizarre.
He's always been so
lazy and dependent,
relying on you to take care
of everything for him.
And now he seems
determined to protect her.
It's like he's actually
getting his act together.
Hey, Mero.
You would probably
finish a lot faster
if you didn't just keep
sweeping the same spot.
Oh.
Well, I guess
I'd better get going.
Yeah.
Everything
my dad said is true.
This is the first time
I've ever seen Chihiro
work so hard in his life.
And the fact that
he's working this hard
for someone other than
himself makes it even weirder.
[school bell rings]
C'mon, this is a huge deal!
"With dramatic spikes in
zombie spottings worldwide,
is humanity doomed to become
a shambling race
of undead ghouls?"
This is my classmate,
Ichie Shinoda.
What?
Everyone knows
zombies don't exist.
And this pillar
of naivety is Miko Yasaka.
I mean it's like, y'know.
If there were actual zombies,
they'd be all over
the news by now.
That glaring omission is proof!
The government is
lying to the people
and covering up information!
Trust me, I read
about it on the internet.
But if zombies were really
about to take over the world,
don't you think that
we would've at least seen
some sign of them by now?
I have!
There are zombies among us.
And they're closer
than you realize!
Y'mean Mero?
No, I didn't mean that close.
Just listen to me!
I'm trying to warn you.
There's a legitimate
cause for concern, here!
The art teacher, Yamanouchi.
Wait, do you mean
Miss Yamanouchi?
Yes, geez!
Miss Yamanouchi!
I remembered that
I'd left something
in the art room as I was
leaving the other day.
But when I went to get it,
it struck me as odd that anyone
would be in there that late.
And that's when I saw it.
There ya go, eat up.
Good boy.
Tasty, isn't it?
You want some more?
She was holding raw meat
dripping with blood
in her bare hands.
And she was feeding it
to something in a bag.
And to make it even weirder.
Y'know, I also noticed something
weird about Miss Yamanouchi.
I walk past the teacher's
lot in the morning,
so I usually see her arrive.
I'd bet my thumb something
was alive in that bag.
There's no way of telling
if it was a zombie,
but whatever it was,
it creeped me out.
Oh! Now that I think about it.
Hah?
I don't know if you
two have noticed it,
but I was just thinking that
she looks really haggard lately.
She looked all skinny and sick
and I was worried
something was wrong with her.
Alright, that settles it!
Yamanouchi is a lumbering,
blood-thirsty zombie!
You're still talking about that?
It's blatantly obvious.
Well, if she's a zombie, what
do you think was in the bag?
Baby?
Or maybe some kind
of zombie underling.
No matter how you add it up,
there's no way it could
possibly be anything else.
So, now that we've narrowed
down all possibilities,
let's get solid
proof she's a zombie!
You want us to get proof?
Well, who else?
It's our duty
as official zombie hunters.
We'll expose the legion
of the undead among us!
We're zombie hunters?
I guess?
Here you go.
Sorry to keep you all cooped up,
but I've got a nice
big dinner here for you.
Now you make sure to fill
your belly all nice and full.
I didn't think
this would be so scary.
How can you be scared?
We're about to see an actual
zombie, this is awesome!
Oh, man, here it comes.
[ALL gasp]
Open wide.
You've got a pet alligator,
Miss Yamanouchi?
I do indeed.
Isn't she so cute?
Maybe?
Sorry, but I've gotta ask.
Why do you bring
your pet alligator to school?
I get worried about
her being alone all day.
You always hear news reports
about alligators getting lost,
and getting found
in the sewers, you know?
Well, that's only a small
part of my reasoning.
The simple truth is
that I hate to spend
even a single minute
away from my sweet girl.
And so naturally,
you stuff her inside a bag
and try to hide her
in the art room.
Yep.
I hate waiting
for the day to end.
But it's so worth it
when it finally does.
Feeding her after school
is my greatest comfort in life!
Uh-huh.
She can be such
a ravenous little monster.
Uh, we were wondering.
Have you not been
feeling well lately?
You look like you've
lost a lotta weight.
You can thank her for that, too.
I've been preparing liver
for her dinner lately.
But it's started
to look so darned delicious.
I actually decided
to share it with her.
And it's really done
a number on my stomach.
How embarrassing.
I assumed I could eat it
like liver sashimi,
but I guess that's what I get
for carelessly eating raw meat.
My stomach's
been in such a state,
I've hardly
been able to eat.
Excuse me.
Hey, Ichie.
Have they been reporting
any more zombie sightings?
Nope.
That's too bad.
Do you wanna hear the crazy
experience I had the other day?
Y'know how I've got such
a super sharp sense of smell?
Did I know that?
It happened yesterday
on my way home from school.
I smelled this really strange
scent wafting down the street.
I don't know how
to properly describe it.
I guess it was like the smell of
a dead human body being boiled.
Whoa, back up.
Miko.
Have you ever actually smelled
a dead human body being boiled?
Where would I have
ever smelled that?
I just imagined that's
what it smells like.
Okay, your imagination
is much more disturbing
than I thought it would be.
Pipe down.
Just let her finish the story.
Please.
So I followed the smell
to where it seemed
like it was coming from.
A small house covered in ivy.
I decided to peek
over the fence.
And then I saw it.
Finally!
About time this story
started to get interesting!
And then what?
Go on.
Well, I just stood there,
frozen from the shock.
But then--
Excuse me, little girl.
Can I help you with something?
Please don't kill me
and eat my brains!
[COUPLE laughing]
That has gotta be the funniest
thing I've ever heard.
That is some wild
imagination you've got on you.
Smelling the soup
and seeing the bones
and thinking we're zombies.
I suppose this means we should
find some zombie customers.
Um.
What kind of soup
smells like that?
My husband quit his job,
and now he's working on
opening up his own ramen shop.
So he's been working
tirelessly, day and night,
7 days a week,
to concoct his very own recipe.
Try it.
Fate has chosen you
as my first patron,
so you've gotta give it a taste.
I know it smells,
but I promise it's delicious.
Go on.
Just a little bite.
Uh... Sure.
I took one bite and
I couldn't even put down
my chopsticks
until it was gone!
If it smelled that bad, then
it must've been tonkotsu style.
Yeah!
It was the first time
I'd ever heard of the stuff!
What exactly is
the point of this story?
Just that it was probably
the best ramen I've ever eaten!
And it had squat
to do with zombies!
Well I bet zombies don't taste
anywhere near as good
as that ramen did.
Why would anyone
ever eat a zombie?
What the hell.
Who would've thought hunting
zombies would be such hard work?
But I remain determined
to find one someday soon!
I wonder what zombies
are actually like anyway.
What do you think
they're like, Mero?
If you really wanna know,
our family's had a zombie
living at our home with us
for a few days now.
Are you serious?
What's the big deal?
Really?
Sweet!
I wanna go see it!
Sure.
But there isn't any guarantee
she'll be at home,
she might be out.
Then take a picture
we can use as evidence!
We can get it published
and be famous!
You don't have
much familiarity
with the concept
of privacy, do you?
Zombies don't deserve
any damn privacy!
You may be right, but my
family's home certainly does.
Please understand there is
a delicate business
side to the temple.
Wait!
Did you just say that
the zombie might be out?
That doesn't sound very safe.
No, from what I can tell,
she knows how to take
care of herself alright.
Not her safety!
Zombies attack people
and eat their flesh, don't they?
No. The only thing I've seen
her eat is hydrangea leaves
so I think she's a vegetarian.
A what?
That is like, the exact
opposite of a normal zombie.
Yeah, I guess that's her game
plan to this whole zombie thing.
She's kind of
irritatingly obsessed
with being a normal girl.
You're not making
any sense here.
Are you sure she's a zombie?
My brother swears that she is.
Him?
The brother who wants
to make out with a zombie?
This is probably
just some weirdo cosplay!
How can you
actually believe him?
There's no way this is
for real, it's gotta be fake.
Whatevs.
Okay, I've gotta get going.
I need to buy some groceries.
Geez, for a second there
I thought we might
actually have a shot at fame.
For real, your brother
is in serious need
of professional help.
You really ought
to tell your mom
to get him a therapist
or something.
Uh. Hey, c'mon, Ichie.
Mero doesn't have a--
Sorry.
Oh.
No big deal,
don't worry about it.
Yeah.
I might as well mention
that my mother is dead.
I was so young
when she passed away
I hardly got
the chance to know her.
So I don't even have fond
memories of her to fall back on.
Although, there is
one memory of her
that sticks out
clearly in my head.
Hello.
And that memory.
Oh, dear.
Are you running
a fever, darling?
Oh!
Would you look at me?
How silly.
I can't tell your temperature
with this bandage on.
Her hand.
[RANKO]
What's the problem?
I just dropped by to
borrow a stupid zombie DVD.
[CHIHIRO] Fine, just hurry
and pick one out, okay?
Geez, alright.
It'd be nice to watch one
together like we used to.
Whatever, just not today.
You've been
kind of a jerk lately.
Huh?
Not like I care though.
Why're you being so weird?
I'm not backing down
without a fight, that's all.
What?
I didn't say anything!
Ugh.
Talking to you is like
putting my brain in a blender.
Maybe your brain's
just rotting.
Like a zombie!
Whoa! Ya think?
Don't look so excited.
I was only making a joke.
I know.
Hmm.
Chihiro thinks our dead mother
is some kind of
zombie Santa Claus.
Good grief.
Why can't he just leave
something normal for a change?
[gong rings]
[bird chirps]
There.
Now that's a proper offering.
[REA] Oh. Hey, Mero.
Hello?
Did you have a good day?
Yeah, I just got home.
Nice to see you, Lady Rea.
Is there something that you're
looking for in the cemetery?
No, nothing in particular.
Chihiro just had an unexpected
guest drop in on him.
So I thought I'd take a walk.
I see.
I dunno.
I can't help but get
a little worried sometimes.
Hmm?
Your family's
done so much for me.
I feel like
I must be such a burden.
No.
It's not like that at all.
Oh, don't feel bad.
I shouldn't have said anything.
So what are you doing out here?
You're visiting someone's grave?
Just saying hello.
To my mother.
I didn't know.
I've been kinda
wondering why your mother
was never around,
but I never imagined that.
I'm so impressed
with you, Mero.
You take care of all
the chores, don't you?
Yeah, it's been my job ever
since I was only a little girl.
My parents always pampered me
and didn't allow me
to do anything.
And you're already so
independent and self-sufficient.
I've got a lot
of respect for you, Mero.
Well.
I wouldn't exactly
bother with all of this
if the guys in my family
could just get their
crap together.
Oh, I know!
It would really
mean a lot to me
if you'd let me help you
with all the chores from now on.
Huh?
No, I can't let you do
that, that's not right.
Why not?
I'm staying here,
so I should help.
I know it sounds strange,
but I actually wanna do them.
Well, is that alright?
What do you think, Mero?
Mero.
What do you think?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, good!
Oh, no.
Is something wrong?
Why are you holding
your head down like that?
You're all flushed.
Are you running a fever?
It's freezing!
Oh.
How silly of me.
I keep forgetting I'm a zombie.
I'll never be able to tell your
temperature with my cold hands.
I love you, Mama!
Mama?
No.
I mean just forget it!
What?
Hold on!
Wait, Mero!
You forgot something!
Thank you, Lady Rea.
Sorry for freaking out.
There!
You're all wrapped up.
Can I help you make supper?
It was strange.
I know why I called her that,
but it's not like me.
Regardless.
I can't deny how
I felt when it happened.
That's a zombie?
I didn't know
they were so pretty.
This is proof, alright.
It's a total fake.
I felt my mother's presence
from the zombie girl
who lives with us.
How come you
look so down, Mero?
Well, Miss Sanka.
Yeah?
Take a hint.
Take a hint!
Huh?
Oh.
Okay.
Next time, on Sankarea,
Episode 10,
"Strong... Feelings..."
Tune in to see Mero!
You know.
I can't help but get the
feeling that you're ungrateful
for Ranko and I helping
you out with this.
Rea! Duck!