This, sucks.
Damn it, Chihiro.
Why do you always have to
make things difficult for me?
Come on, you slow poke!
Slow down!
You're runnin' too fast!
Geez, I'm gonna
leave you behind!
No!
Wait up, you meanie!
[RANKO crying]
Here you go.
Oh wow! Looks tasty.
It's so pretty.
Yes, it is.
But not too pretty to eat.
My name's Ranko Saoji.
I'm a sophomore at the
prestigious Sanka Academy.
This is my family's restaurant,
the Saoji Kaiseki Kitchen.
My mom manages the place
and my dad is the head chef.
I guess you could say
the restaurant business
is in my blood.
I've been helping out
at the restaurant
since I was barely
old enough to walk,
so I'm a handy fill-in
on days like this
when the staff
is short-handed.
Thank you, come back soon!
Chop, chop!
We've got people out there
waiting for those, y'know.
Oh, shut up.
And don't startle me!
I could cut off a finger.
Just be thankful
I'm here, alright?
I don't need you
ridin' my ass all day.
This is not how I wanted
to spend my Sunday.
Yeah right, you know you're
happy to spend it with me!
You've been a grouch
since we were kids.
Now get back to work!
You're the one
who interrupted me!
Only to tell you to
stop being so lazy!
Listen to you.
You kids sound like an old,
married couple when you argue.
Mom, gross!
Don't worry, Chihiro,
I don't expect you to take over
the family business
when you two get married.
But we'll make sure to leave it
to you in our will when we die
just in case you
change your mind.
Isn't that right, dear?
What is wrong with you?
Geez.
Hey!
Be careful, okay?
I will. Thank you.
Whoa! It's gettin' hot in here!
You don't have to
act like touching me
is the worst thing in the world.
Say what?
Nothing, forget it!
I've known Chihiro
since I was a kid.
I met him when
I was in kindergarten.
Y'know how it is in
romantic comedies?
The protagonists
are introduced
and they immediately
hate each other,
but then they
suddenly realize
that they've fallen
hopelessly in love?
Well, the first time
I met Chihiro,
It was nothing like that.
Aren't you afraid?
No, there's nothin'
to be scared of.
I thought I'd been
rescued by a genuine prince.
Imagine my
surprise the next day,
when my uncle Do'on
introduced him as my cousin.
Well, Ranko.
I'd like you to
meet my son, Chihiro.
He's a year younger than you,
but I'm sure you two
will have a good time.
You wanna play?
It'll be fun!
I'd made up my mind.
And I was determined
to be friends with him.
Alright!
We're watching a movie?
Yeah. It's a good one, too.
Okay.
Is something
the matter, Adriana?
Oh, did you have
a bad dream, baby?
Adriana?
[RANKO screaming]
Hey, Chihiro. Chihiro!
What?
Let's go play outside.
Why?
'Cuz I wanna play outside, okay?
Sounds boring.
Let's go play outside.
So, what kinda stuff do you
like to do for fun, Chihiro?
Watch zombie movies.
No, I mean other than that.
Read zombie movie magazines.
Do you only like zombies?
I like eating, too.
That's silly, eating isn't
somethin' you do for fun.
[CHIHIRO laughs]
So pretty!
I've got an idea!
Let's play house
and we can use these to--
What the heck are
you doing, Chihiro?
I read that sometimes they bury
dead bodies under cherry trees.
Huh?
Maybe we'll find
a zombie down here.
What?
But I don't wanna find one!
I'm scared of zombies!
Hey.
Isn't that Chihiro
from the temple?
Think so.
Whoa is he playing
with that girl over there?
Ew, gross!
He knows there's no way
we'd play with him,
so he had to get
a girl to instead!
What a loser!
Quit messin' with him,
you bullies!
You're just jealous 'cause you
don't get to play house with me!
Chihiro?
[CHIHIRO crying]
Where are you going?
There go the waterworks!
Is there anything
that doesn't make him cry?
Maybe he thinks
it's okay for boys to cry.
I'd convinced myself
he was a prince
when he was actually
just a zombie-loving weirdo.
He was awkward,
lazy, antisocial.
Not to mention a total crybaby!
He wasn't scared of graveyards
'cause he'd seen 'em
in his zombie movies.
Well, that, and there
were graves in his backyard.
In one afternoon.
Chihiro had gone from my prince
to a creep that I never
wanted to see again.
It's a shame you
can't stay longer.
Yeah, but it's for the best
because with
the way we let loose,
you probably need
a break, don't you?
Well, you'll have to
be sure to come visit us
when festival time
starts up again.
Thank you, we'll definitely try.
Hey, couldn't Izuna make it?
Unfortunately, Mero came down
with a fever late last night,
so she took her to the hospital.
Oh, that's terrible.
I wish we'd had the chance
to see her before we took off.
Don't worry about it.
I'll tell her you said goodbye.
Well, brother.
See you later.
Hey, Ranko.
Don't you want to say goodbye
to your new buddy Chihiro?
No.
What the hell?
Your parents called me
in to help in the kitchen,
so how come I'm stuck out here
making deliveries with you?
Because you're not exactly
what I'd consider
helpful in the kitchen.
Well that's not my fault.
I've only held a kitchen knife
like two times in my life.
That explains it,
but it doesn't excuse it.
So, what made you decide
to tag along with me?
I don't think it's a good idea
for you to greet
the restaurant's
customers on your own.
You're not exactly
the most articulate guy,
if you know what I mean.
Oh, c'mon,
I'm not a total idiot.
I think I can handle
a simple greeting.
Can it, Chihiro!
Quit your bellyaching
and just do your job, young man!
Thank you, Ranko.
I appreciate it.
Don't be silly,
you know I don't mind coming by.
Please don't hesitate
to work that lazy bum
I call a son as
hard as possible.
As much as you do for us,
it's only fair.
I'll whip him into shape,
no problem.
Uh, shouldn't I have some kind
of say in this hard-work issue?
Uh-uh.
No.
Silly me.
So, how many stops we have left?
Two more.
Why?
Is helping me
really that terrible?
C'mon, you know
it's not like that.
I'm just worried about Rea.
Oh yeah.
Your zombie girlfriend.
Wanko, I thought
I made it clear
there's nothin'
going on between us.
There are just all sorts
of uncertain
variables I'm worried about.
I dunno.
I guess things haven't
really stabilized yet.
I see what's going on.
You do?
It's obvious that you're worried
'cause you've totally
got the hots for her.
What the--?
You aren't even listening to me.
Are you?
This is so not fair, Furuya!
How come you get to go on
a date with a hot chick?
Huh?
What?
Are you two really on a date?
Of course not.
Don't be an idiot.
Geez, don't be rude!
How's he supposed to know
whether we're on a date or not?
Well, it's not and
that's all that matters.
Really?
Is it that horrible for someone
to think you're on date with me?
What in the hell
is wrong with you today?
Stop right there!
Don't deny it, because
I know how to recognize
a lover's spat when I see one!
Well, you're wrong.
Damn you!
First Rea and now Ranko?
What could such epic hotties
possibly see in a dope like you?
And the ironic cruelty of
your sick zombie fixation
is too much for me to bear!
Is it your charm?
Or your fashion sense?
You're doing this
to mock me, aren't you?
Well you've succeeded!
Come on, Yasutaka, calm down!
How can I be calm
when he stole my dream?
You're officially delusional.
Ranko, would you
please explain to me
what the hell you
see in this guy.
He's a creepy nerd who's
obsessed with zombies,
isn't remotely handsome,
is a rude and lazy
slacker, and a coward.
Yeah, that sounds like Chihiro.
Wow really?
Gee, thanks.
That's some harsh
judgment coming from a guy
who pervs out over
any pretty girl he sees.
Yeah, so what?
I take pride in my adoration
of beautiful women!
And it's killing me that every
single one of 'em is into you!
You're wrong, dude.
Where are you getting this crap?
You keep denying but I can
see it with my own eyes!
Would the two of
you please calm down?
Look at me,
I'm perfectly calm, Mogi.
After our first meeting,
I didn't see Chihiro
again for two years,
and we picked up
right where we left off.
Shortly after I turned six,
my dad made the decision
to move the family restaurant
from our previous home
in Chiba to here in Shiyo.
Just a stone's throw
from the Furuya family temple.
After we got settled in,
my mom invited Chihiro
to come play one afternoon.
Even though my crush on him
had gone up in smoke,
our parents were determined
for us to be friends,
so I gave it a shot.
Hey, Chihiro.
Wanna play?
I've got some games.
Nah.
Well then we can
go play outside.
Nah.
He hasn't changed at all.
Here, I brought some
snacks for you kiddos.
Now, Chihiro.
You're our neighborhood
welcoming committee.
So you've gotta play
nice with Ranko, 'kay?
Oh, just look how bashful he is.
You're so adorable!
I don't know why, but my mom
liked Chihiro from the get go.
So she was always
pushing us to get along
which made the situation
even more unbearable.
Hey, stop it.
C'mon.
Ew, ew, ew
Oh, you don't
like that, Chihiro.
No, just look
at this pouty face.
Such a cute face, look at him.
Right, Ranko?
Why the long face, kiddo?
Where'd Chihiro go?
He's reading a
monster magazine.
Why dontcha go upstairs
and get him to play with you?
Because he says he doesn't
want to play with me.
He doesn't like games
and won't go outside.
Well, then why
don't you take him
to the video store and pick out
a movie for you to watch?
Yeah.
Didn't you say there
was some new anime
out that you've
been wanting to see?
The two of you can go rent
that and watch it together.
Okay?
Ranko, I know you're not the
kind of girl who's gonna leave
her little cousin all alone
when he comes over to visit you.
I'll give it a try.
It's down this way.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, where did you go?
[RANKO screams]
Chihiro, you're in
the horror section!
So?
I wanna get an anime.
It's a good one.
I promise you'll like it.
There's no way
it can beat this!
[RANKO gasps]
[RANKO screams]
Look!
Zombie Academy,
School Festival of Horror.
Yep.
You sure know how
to pick 'em, Chihiro.
But I've got one
you haven't seen yet.
I brought it back from my trip
to America and it's pretty sick.
Wanna see it?
You know it!
I tell ya, that little
guy is an incredible kid.
Only five years old
and he's a downright
encyclopedia of horror movies.
There.
Uh, this one's pretty hardcore,
so try to keep it
from your parents, okay?
Right.
Hey.
What's hardcore mean?
It means it's good and
shows all the awesome stuff.
I guess I like awesome stuff.
Yeah, it's gonna be really cool.
Guts and brains.
We were supposed to go and
pick something out together.
Just trust me on this.
It's way better
than some silly anime.
This whole series
is top-notch horror.
Whatever, you know I don't
even like horror movies.
I bet this is gonna be
the one that changes your mind.
But it's in
a different language.
You don't have to understand
the words for it to be fun.
Maybe for you,
but it's not fun for me!
I wanna watch an anime
that I can understand!
I promise this is way
cooler than some anime!
How many times do I have to tell
you I don't like scary movies?
I'm taking this one back!
Huh?
Hey, wait up!
[DOG growls]
[RANKO gasps]
Come on, Ranko!
[DOG growls]
[DOG barks]
[RANKO whimpering]
[DOG barking]
[CHIHIRO whimpering]
[CHIHIRO yelling]
Get away from her,
you dirty mutt!
[CHIHIRO grunting and yelling]
[DOG growling]
You saved my life.
[RANKO and CHIHIRO crying]
I'm proud of you.
The way you saved me back
there was really brave.
Thinking back on it now...
That first time I met
him in the cemetery,
it was love at first sight.
[ACTRESS] You mean
you'll stay with me?
[ACTOR] Of course I will.
[RANKO] And by
the time I was ten,
there was no denying it.
I had fallen flat on
my face in love with Chihiro.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What?
I'm just curious.
Have you thought
about your first kiss?
Like what you want
it to be like?
Depends what
you mean by 'be like'?
Well, y'know, there's all
sorts of different ways.
Standing on a cliff
by the sea at sunset.
A passionate goodbye
at the train station.
Like that.
I dunno.
I guess I'd want my first kiss
to be with a hot zombie chick.
What?
Are you serious?
You don't actually believe
there's a zombie girl
out there, do you?
I dunno there might be.
Aw c'mon, would ya give
me a serious answer?
Your first kiss is a very
important thing, y'know!
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Geez!
Furuya!
Mark my words, one day you're
gonna get what's comin' to ya!
Or you could just introduce me
to a girl, that's cool, too!
Man.
I've got some annoying friends.
Alright, let's take care
of these last two stops.
Chihiro.
Here take my hand.
What?
Why would I do that?
Because I told you to, okay?
Okay, okay, I'll do it!
Alright then, let's go.
What the hell is
goin' on with you?
Chihiro.
Yeah?
Knowing you, you probably don't,
but do you remember
the first time we held hands?
Actually, I do.
It was the first time
we met, right?
I found you crying
in the cemetery
and I had to take you by the
hand to lead you out of there.
Wait.
Is that what happened?
I don't know,
was that the first time?
Yeah, I can't really remember
that far back,
that's why I asked you.
Seriously what
is with you today?
Man, girls are weird.
Well, that's
the last one for the day.
You deliver to some
pretty swanky houses.
Right?
The old lady that lives here
had us cater a memorial service
for one of her relatives
a few years back
and now she's a loyal customer
who orders delivery
from us almost every day.
You've officially made it
through a whole day of work.
Guess you can go home now.
Really?
We're past our
peak hours for the day,
and there's really nothing else
for you to do back
at the restaurant.
You'd just be
standing around bored.
You mean I'm free?
It's about damn time!
See ya later!
What's up?
Are you okay, Wanko?
Why do you have
to look so disgusted
when I'm coming in for a kiss?
Did'ya think about
how that makes me feel?
You know how important
a kiss is to me!
I really...
I don't wanna lose...
I'm not gonna let
her take him from me!
'Cause I belong with Chihiro!
And you're sure that it's
alright for me to do this?
You did get Mero's
explicit permission, right?
Well, as long as
she's okay with it.
Cool, here we go.
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 7,
"Counterfeit... Freedom..."
What?
Mero?
What the hell is this?
I wanna speak to the producer!
I'm sorry!
They said you were cool with it!
You guys better
explain this to me
or it's going
to get ugly in here!