Chihiro, no!
[DAN'ICHIRO]
This works out perfectly.
There are so many things
he and I need to discuss.
Isn't that right, Furuya?
They say green
is a healing color.
Welcome Mr. Furuya.
We're so glad you could
join us this afternoon.
I thought you might be thirsty
so I brought you a drink.
Oh, thank you.
You're the nicest kidnapper
a guy could ever ask for.
Now how 'bout you cut
the crap and untie me, lady?
I hope you enjoy
your beverage, sir.
Wait!
Don't go!
You can't just leave me here!
Untie me, now!
Sorry!
I'll stop yelling.
I can't believe she left.
If that's how you're gonna be
then I take back what
I said about not yelling.
In fact, I'm gonna
yell even louder!
I know you can
hear me out there!
What am I supposed to
do if my back itches?
Uh-oh, I can feel it coming on.
You gonna come
scratch it for me or what?
I'm gonna keep
yelling 'til you do!
You're back.
I knew the noise
would get to ya.
Would you lower your voice?
I can hear you yelling from
the other end of the hallway.
Hey, wait a minute.
Who the heck are you?
I find it rather insulting
that you have to ask.
Especially since
you're in my home.
I'm not here
because I want to be.
That much is obvious.
I'm Dan'ichiro's wife,
Mrs. Sanka.
But you can call me Aria.
Oh, then you must
be Rea's mother.
And you must be the Furuya boy
I've heard so much about.
You're the poor schmuck
who got stuck babysitting her,
aren't you?
Well, yeah.
but I wouldn't really
call it "babysitting."
So, how far have you gotten
with little miss perfect?
Surely you two have
at least kissed by now.
Have you made it
to third base yet?
On second thought, as repressed
as that girl's been.
I would bet she's positively
insatiable, isn't she?
Whoa.
I don't know what
you're trying to say.
But Rea's not like that.
Oh really?
Well... that is a shame.
I thought you would've
sealed the deal by now.
On the other hand,
I can't say I blame you.
I suppose it would be
rather disconcerting
to make-out with a monster.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
She's a walking corpse, right?
And if she's already
started decaying,
she must be letting off
a pretty foul stench.
Her skin's probably a mess, too.
Real funny, huh?
Your own flesh and blood
becoming a zombie.
Excuse me.
What did you say?
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
I've never actually had
any "flesh-and-blood"
children of my own.
But... you're Rea's...
I mean...
Well, aren't you?
No, I am not.
I happen to be
Dan'ichiro Sanka's second wife.
Shocking, isn't it?
She is simply a product
of his previous marriage.
There's absolutely no blood
relation between us whatsoever.
If that were true, she would've
told me something about it.
I highly doubt that.
The Sanka family is great
at hiding their dirty,
little secrets.
There are only a handful
of people who know.
I'm no good at
keeping secrets.
But I'm not related, in fact,
I used to be one of their maids.
Don't get any ideas.
I don't want you thinking
that I'm of humble
origins or anything.
In the years
leading up to Rea's birth
the Sanka family carefully
handpicked each of their maids.
You see, we weren't
just the household help,
we were potential
marriage candidates
for their precious heir.
They analyzed our bloodlines,
education, and cultural standing
before we could even
be considered for employment.
There were many applicants,
but very few made the cut.
This might be
the only room in the mansion
that doesn't have
a picture on the wall.
In that case,
I'll take this opportunity
to display one of my own.
Ever since Dan'ichiro was a boy,
he's had a legion of maids
throwing themselves
at him in the hopes of one day
joining his affluent family.
But much to their chagrin,
he never showed any signs
of attraction towards them.
The Sanka family hired me
as one of their household maids
when Dan'ichiro
was a graduate student.
[WALLA: MAIDS]
I hate to break it to you but
everything you went through
to work here was
a waste of time.
The heir isn't all that fond of
women if you know what I mean.
You're going to languish
here like the rest of us.
Did you ever stop to think
that maybe he is fond of women,
but he's simply not
interested in any of you?
Why you!
Perhaps I was overconfident,
but I had never met
a man I couldn't seduce.
[bell ringing]
[ARIA knocking on door]
You may enter.
[door opens and closes]
How did you know
that I wanted more coffee?
You tend to go through
it quickly when you're studying.
I also brought a lap
blanket for you.
And your name?
My name is Aria, sir.
[DAN'ICHIRO panting]
It wasn't long
before he called me
to his side more
than the other maids.
[door opens and closes]
In the end,
my persistence did little
to sway his heart
in my direction.
Master Dan'ichiro.
Good morning.
Right.
I began to wonder if
the rumors I'd heard were true.
Perhaps he wasn't
interested in women after all.
Then the situation
was turned on its ear.
In the name of social welfare,
the Sanka family invited
the disadvantaged
and institutionalized
to the mansion,
and a fencing tournament
was held in their honor.
Naturally, Dan'ichiro
was one of the contestants.
[CROWD] Wow!
[buzzer buzzes]
[crowd cheers and applauds]
Oh, wow! The Master's
such a magnificent fencer!
Yeah, he looked amazing
out there, didn't he?
C'était un bon match.
[DAN'ICHIRO growls]
Next time you'd better
fight like you mean it.
You don't have to throw
the match to lose to me!
[ARIA] The Sanka family
is a major contributor
to an international
fencing society.
In fact, they're
the primary sponsors.
Therefore, it was
decided the Sanka heir
would always be the winner
of the annual tournament.
Unfortunately, Dan'ichiro wasn't
able to read between the lines,
so the custom
didn't sit well with him.
When the tournament was over,
the fencers lined up to thank
their special guests
for attending.
That's when a young lady
went up to Dan'ichiro.
Excuse me, you dropped this.
Yeah.
Thanks a lot.
I can tell you're disappointed
about how your match played out.
But you shouldn't
mistreat your things.
Not everyone is
as fortunate as you are.
If you're lucky enough
to have nice things,
you should take
good care of them.
Life can be full of trials
but don't let your frustration
get the best of you.
Just keep your chin up.
A few days later.
Dan'ichiro found
that 15-year-old girl
and asked for her
hand in marriage.
The Sanka family
was shocked, of course.
As were all the other maids
who had served him in
the hopes of winning his heart.
Apparently, proper social
standing meant nothing.
He pushed us aside and chose
that child to be his wife.
And let me guess, that girl was
Rea's real mother, wasn't she?
The Sanka family fiercely
opposed the marriage.
They were determined
to talk some sense
into their befuddled heir.
But Dan'ichiro
had made his decision
and there was nothing they
could say to change his mind.
Her social status is an issue?
You are the Sanka family heir!
You can't marry a girl
from an unknown family!
In that case, I shall
renounce my position as heir.
By doing so, I'll be free
to marry whomever I choose.
Please think about what
you're saying, Dan'ichiro.
You're being ridiculous!
You would
abandon your own family
just to be with that cripple?
That "cripple"?
You'd better watch
your mouth from now on.
I won't have anyone
disrespecting her.
I understand you're
upset with my decision
to forsake the Sanka family
in the name of love.
However I will not tolerate
anyone insulting
my future wife in such a manner!
Once his relatives
had been silenced,
Dan'ichiro went on
to marry the girl.
Unfortunately, she passed
away soon after Rea was born.
Dan'ichiro fell
into a deep depression.
He couldn't sleep or eat.
I knew something had to
be done or he would die.
I did everything
I could to bear him up,
and gradually
he began to recover.
Dan'ichiro rewarded my diligence
by asking me to be his wife.
I became more
and more despondent
as each of our wedding
anniversaries passed.
In all that time, Dan'ichiro had
yet to look upon me as his wife.
What does that mean exactly?
You're as dumb
as you look, aren't you?
It means that he never
made love to me.
It didn't take
me long to realize.
The only reason he married
me in the first place
is because Rea needed a mother.
But she didn't.
Her father was hands-on and did
everything for his little girl.
There was nothing for me
to do but sit and watch them.
I was always on the outside
watching the two of them
from a distance.
I never felt as though
I was a member of their family.
What is it now, Aria?
I was wondering if we
could go on a vacation.
Well, we never had a honeymoon,
and we don't get
to spend much time together.
I thought it'd be nice.
Yes, it would be.
Now that you mention it,
I've always thought
it would be good
for Rea to start traveling
at an early young age.
Wait, we have to take
her along with us?
Well, of course.
Why wouldn't we?
Despite the evidence
to the contrary.
I honestly believed
Dan'ichiro had chosen me
to be his second
wife out of love.
Look at me, Daddy!
Mama!
I want a picture with you,
me, and Daddy together!
That's fine with me.
I believed Dan'ichiro's
love for Rea was no different
than the love any father
would feel for his daughter.
But I was wrong.
Would you mind telling me
why you've asked me here?
I'm getting impatient.
Well? Answer me.
It's not my place,
but I thought that I should give
you some advice, Madam Aria.
You're wasting
your time trying to win
Master Dan'ichiro's affections.
His heart already
belongs to another.
What are you talking about?
I must ask that you
not raise your voice, ma'am.
I don't want the master to hear.
It's a pretty blanket, Daddy!
This is how
I'd like you to pose, okay?
Keep your feet pointed.
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry you had to
find out this way, Madam.
I was disgusted with him.
I knew exactly
why he was doing it.
Because he couldn't
let go of the love
that he felt for his first wife!
Everybody thinks that
vapid girl is my daughter.
When in truth, the sight
of her makes my stomach turn.
As if her old man
weren't bad enough.
Rea had to deal with
this basket case, too.
Well, now that you've
heard my side of the story
you understand what
a tragic life I've led.
I haven't been touched in ages,
but now that you're
here we can change that.
Yeah.
Feels good, doesn't it?
You can't get this kind of body
heat from your dead girlfriend.
Uh.
I'm real sorry about that.
But I'm afraid I'm only
interested in zombie girls.
What is it about
that little bitch?
She's not half the woman I am!
Why won't anyone
pay attention to me?
How the hell did you
get in here, kitty?
Dan'ichiro would die if he knew
there was a cat in
the mansion but who cares?
I could use a friend right now.
Sweet, kitty.
You wanna live with me?
That sweet kitty's
a zombie, too.
Someone get these
troublemakers out of here!
I will not have them
playing with my emotions!
If I'm free to leave,
I'd be happy to get out of here;
I just need someone to untie me.
I'm sorry, but that's
not going to happen.
Master Dan'ichiro
is expecting you.
You think I care?
Who the hell does
your boss think
he is kidnapping me
and holding me hostage?
Huh?
Being the head of
the Sanka family
may give him more power
than the general population.
But no matter
how powerful he is,
he still isn't above the law.
Thanks for helping me out.
Hey, while you're at it,
would ya mind untying me?
Sorry, no can do.
Didn't think so.
Lucky you.
I'll admit, I'm jealous.
He's asked that
you spend time with him.
He never asked me.
I'm his wife and yet he would
rather spend time talking
to you than to me.
Um, excuse me,
could you please
turn the air conditioner up
as high as it'll go?
Sure thing.
I didn't think it was
all that warm out.
I just know those brutes
were sent by Father.
Who else would want
to kidnap Chihiro?
I've got to save him
before it's too late!
I'm sorry sir, but could
you go a little faster?
Whatever you say, miss.
I'm startin' to wonder if this
girl even has cash on her.
Please wait here, Mr. Furuya.
Why do I have to wait?
I thought "Master Dan'ichiro"
was expecting me.
Yes, he will be
with you momentarily.
Huh?
Hey! Come back!
I took these stunning
photographs myself.
Sick bastard.
I wish I could credit their
beauty to my photography,
but I had little to do with it.
I'm inspired by my subject.
Rea is a dazzling light
in a dark world.
innocence personified.
There is nothing
that terrifies me more
than the thought of losing her.
But, thanks to you,
I had quite an epiphany.
I had to lose her to realize
how much her love means to me.
I'm more determined than ever to
protect her from cads like you.
I'll prove that I'm
the only man she needs!
Thank you.
I'm grateful.
But you will pay for this.
Chihiro Furuya!
Okay, enough with
the temper tantrums.
Pull yourself
together and get with it.
Work is work.
You've already accepted the job
so it's not like you
can pout your way out of it.
Fine, I'll start.
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 11,
"Nothing... Really...
Special." There, I did it.
If you're not gonna do it
right then why even bother?
At least give 'em your
"tune in to see Mero" line!