[Television]
Zombies!
Creatures that've been
brought back to life
with the use of dark
magic or secret potions.
They are said
to roam the Earth
feasting on
the flesh of the living.
They are terrifying.
Monsters!
[BABU] There's a girl who
lives in our peaceful town
who's keeping a dark secret.
She's a zombie!
[REA gasps]
Babu!
Don't sneak up
on me like that!
You nearly
scared me to death!
[BABU] I, too,
am a zombie. Babu!
What? Wanna join me?
[BABU] We are
the living dead.
C'mere.
You could use a bath, too.
But let's get those
bandages off first.
[BABU] We were
unfortunate enough
to lose our lives at a young age
due to unforeseen accidents.
Thankfully, an incredible
elixir allowed us
to be reborn as zombies.
The person
responsible for that elixir.
is my master, Chihiro Furuya.
Oh!
Hey Babu! I'm home!
Ya miss me?
Luckily for us, he considers
himself a devotee of the undead.
He's a zombie fanatic
and he's had plenty
of practice making potions.
I got some more dry ice
to keep your body cool.
Hey Chihiro!
Didya have a good day today?
Geez!
You know, you don't have
to shower all the time,
you're a freakin' zombie now!
I know.
But still...
We aren't like all
the other unhygienic zombies,
we prefer to stay clean.
Right, Babu?
[BABU] To be honest,
I don't particularly care
whether I bathe or not.
It'd be nice if I could
open up the wound on my belly
and scrub everything
on the inside, too!
I don't think that's a good
idea considering those stitches
are the only thing keeping your
intestines from popping out.
There.
Here you go, Babu.
Have some hydrangea leaves.
[BABU] I've always lived here
as the Furuya family's housecat.
The girl, on the other hand,
ran away from home
when she became a zombie.
That's how she ended up
living here, too.
It's so beautiful outside.
She spent her youth living
under the watchful eye of
her overprotective father.
But all she wanted was to live
the life of a normal girl.
Hey, Chihiro?
Whaddya say we go for a walk?
We can be back by suppertime.
What'd I tell you?
You shouldn't expose
yourself to the elements!
I explained what happens
to the body when you die.
Don't you remember?
Lemme see.
You said amino acids
increase because
proteins start to
decompose and so
the body becomes more savory!
That's gotta be it, right?
I wouldn't know if it
affects their flavor.
Nasty.
Now think back, remember how
just a few hours after you died
you couldn't move
your body anymore?
That's called rigor mortis.
It causes the limbs of a corpse
to become rigid and stiff.
I see.
So it's kinda like when you
take a fish that just died,
turn it into sashimi,
and then it gets crunchy.
It's impossible to talk
to you when you're hungry.
Now listen.
Once rigor mortis has passed,
the body will then
gradually begin to uh...
Never mind.
Just try not to spend
too much time outside
while the sun
is still up, okay?
If you say so.
[BABU] While my
master is concerned
about preserving
the girl's zombified-body,
he also understands her desire
to go out and enjoy
her newfound freedom.
Fine, let's go.
But we can't stay out long.
[BABU]
This experience has changed
my master
for the better.
He's much more dependable now
than he ever was
during my lifetime.
Wow, it's so
beautiful out today!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Sorry, I couldn't help it.
Geez.
I get that you're excited about
going back to school and all,
but you've really gotta be more
careful with your body, Rea.
Yes, sir!
Well, the sun's
not at its peak yet.
Guess she'll be okay.
You got it from here?
Uh-huh.
I'll see ya later on.
I hate to be a nag but try to
stay out of direct sunlight.
and don't forget to
eat your hydrangea leaves.
I know!
If I don't eat them
I'll be in big trouble, right?
After all, they're
maintaining my body.
Got it!
Don't worry about me!
Okay. I'll try.
Have a good day, Chihiro!
I'll see you at home!
Aw crap.
That's my cue to go.
There's that guy.
Yeah, he's such a weirdo, right?
Wanko!
Well... what's this?
Are you transferring
to Sanka Girl's Academy?
Oh, you're so funny.
I walked Rea to school to
make sure she got here okay.
That's nice of you.
I have early morning tennis
practice every day, you know.
Think you can walk
me to school, too?
I'm such a delicate young lady.
You're a lot of things
but delicate ain't one.
Alright, that does it!
You're done!
[CHIHIRO yells]
Good morning, Miss Matsukida.
Oh, good morning,
Miss Onozawa.!
The same to you, Miss Sanka.
You look pretty today,
Miss Sanka.
Oh, thank you, Miss Kusakabe.
Rea! Wait up!
It's so good to see you!
I was worried you were
never coming back to school!
Oh. Hello Heren!
Glad to be here!
How're you?
Oh, I'm good!
A little tired after
morning tennis practice
but that's because I have to
be there at the crack of dawn.
I'm kinda surprised
I've stuck with it.
Oh really?
You must enjoy it, huh?
Yeah, I do.
But I hate that it leaves
me drenched in sweat!
I'm gonna go and take
a quick shower now.
I'll see you in class, kay?
Wait!
Well, if it isn't Miss Sanka.
Good morning.
Ms. Morizono!
I didn't see you there.
You must be doing better if
you've come back to school.
I was worried because
you seemed to be getting
more and more
depressed each day,
but now, you've got
a happy glow about you.
Sorry.
I didn't realize
it was so obvious.
Tell me something, Miss Sanka.
You haven't fallen in love
with a young man, now have you?
[REA gasps]
Don't be upset!
I'm teasing.
[tennis ball explodes]
[MORIZONO gasps]
I, uh...
Well, I, I guess that
must've been an old ball.
Please excuse me.
[BABU] It's said that human
muscles perform at 20 to 30%
of their capacity because of
limitations set by the brain.
However, those
limitations disappear
once you
become a zombie.
We have superhuman
strength because our muscles
perform at their full
capacity all the time.
[girls cheer]
[whistle blows]
That was awesome!
Who'd have known she
was so great at basketball?
She made a slam dunk
without even breaking a sweat!
I hope Rea's okay.
She better not be overdoin' it.
She wants to be
a "normal girl," huh?
Hey.
What the heck are you
babblin' to yourself about?
We're high school kids,
not like we have any stress.
You'd be surprised.
Unlike you, I've got all kinds
of problems I gotta deal with.
You know, now
that you mention it.
I have noticed that Furuya's
been acting differently lately.
Maybe he's just maturing
faster than the rest of us.
Wha--?
How can the guy who's
in love with zombies
be more mature than us?
Hey, Yasutaka.
Let's say, you had a
date with a normal girl,
what kinda activities
would you have planned?
Huh?
Sorry.
I didn't mean
to catch you off guard,
I just asked because I thought
you might know, that's all.
Wow, I never
thought I'd see the day
you'd fall for
one of the living.
You! How dare you?
Whoa, what's your problem?
Alright spill it!
Who is she?
What?
You sneaky bastard.
Don't tell me you're tryin'
to get your grubby hands on Rea?
It's not Ranko, is it?
Or maybe an incestuous
crush on Mero?
You disgust me, man!
No, it's nothing like that!
Lemmo go!
I can't believe it.
Just when you think
you really know a person.
You better watch your step or
I'm gonna knock your teeth in!
[BABU] From what I can tell,
the life of a human
can be incredibly stressful
and rather complicated.
I'll stick to the leisurely life
of a cat, thank you very much.
[tires screeching]
[BABU meows]
Thank goodness you're okay!
I was so worried I had run
you over, little kitty!
Well, aren't you just precious.
[female cat meows]
[BABU flirtily meows]
[REA] Wait 'til you hear this!
So we were playing
this game "basketball"
in gym class today
and I made a--
wait, what's it called?
Oh yeah!
Can you believe I
made a grand slam?
I think what you're trying
to say is slam-dunk, Rea.
Yeah! That's it!
All of the other girls
were so shocked.
Zombie power is
pretty amazing, isn't it?
Hold on.
You went to gym class today?
You shouldn't be straining your
bones and muscles like that.
Just because you
don't feel any pain
doesn't mean it's
not doing damage.
You've gotta be more careful!
Yeah. I know.
I promise you I'll take
it easy next time, okay?
Geez.
I don't think you get
how serious this is.
Uh-oh.
Looks like rain.
Seems weird to sit here like
this doing absolutely nothing.
It's boring but we've gotta wait
for this rain to lighten up.
C'mon, live a little, Chihiro!
The sun is hidden
behind the rain clouds,
and the temperature's fallen,
it's the perfect weather for me!
I think we should go
for a little walk.
No way!
Don't worry.
I'm a zombie so it's not like
I'm gonna catch a cold.
See?
I'm avoiding puddles
just for you!
Hey, careful jumping like that
or you'll trip on somethin'!
[BABU] The poor thing had
to die and become a zombie
just to be able to behave with
the exuberance of a normal girl.
[REA] This is so cool.
I just realized I can
touch bugs and snails
whenever I want to now.
I wasn't allowed to play
with them when I was alive
because my father
was such a germaphobe.
Nobody's stopping me now.
Guess that makes me one step
closer to being a normal girl.
Yeah.
[BABU] It's hard for my master
to keep up the façade.
'Cause he knows
she'll never be "normal."
[BABU meows]
[cat meows]
[cat flirtily meows]
[BABU meows proudly]
[CHIHIRO yawns]
[REA] I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have made you
come walking with me
when you're tired.
No.
I should apologize.
I just wish I could do more
than take you out for walks.
Well, in that case,
think I could convince you
to go to school with me?
Huh?
I bet if you disguised
yourself as a student.
You'd have no trouble
sneaking in to my school.
Are you asking me to
dress up like a girl?
Never know, you might be
surprised by how good you look.
Ugh, I don't know how I'm
supposed to respond to that.
I love the nighttime.
When I was alive, that's
when we would meet up.
At night.
Right about this time remember?
Yeah, I do.
It's so pretty!
Check it out!
You can see the whole town
from up here, Chihiro!
Be careful!
I don't want you gettin'
excited and falling over.
I'm a zombie, silly!
Even I did fall, it's not like
it'd hurt me or anything.
I realize that but there's
more at stake here
than whether
you'd feel any pain.
Now that you're a zombie, if
you get seriously injured then.
I know, I know.
My body can't heal itself.
I'd be stuck with those wounds.
That's right.
Just like the wound on my tummy,
you can sew it shut
but it'll never heal.
Even so.
I can't be scared.
I wanna make the most
of every moment.
It would be a shame to leave
this world with any regrets.
[BABU] It's common knowledge
that cellular metabolism
ceases almost immediately
after a creature dies.
Once a living thing is incapable
of producing new cells
and expelling old ones,
it's impossible to sustain life.
Except in the case of a zombie.
The effects of the reanimation
drug they've been given
will help sustain their
body to a certain degree.
But there's no longer any
active production of new cells.
In other words.
Even though we remain conscious
and don't feel any pain.
There is no denying
that gradually.
Our bodies are decaying.
Slow down!
You're moving too fast!
Thanks a lot, Rea.
No problem.
You've gotta be more
careful too, you know.
I'd be heartbroken if
anything ever happened to you.
Huh?  Oh, really?
[BABU] It's not
just our bodies,
but our minds too,
that gradually...
Gradually...
[BABU meows]
Hey there, Babu!
Perfect timing.
I just finished putting some
more dry ice in your bed for ya.
Goodness, look at you.
Someone's becoming
a spoiled little kitty.
That cat.
What's up with him?
[BABU meowing]
[REA laughing]
Bye Babu!
We'll see you when we get home!
Hey!
Watch yourself!
Try to stay in the shade
while the sun's out!
[BABU] Nothing in this world
ever goes the way
you want it to,
it doesn't matter
whether you're alive or dead.
I'm sure those two still have
a tough road ahead of them.
But I'm going to enjoy
every last moment
I have on this Earth.
Until my body wastes away.
[BABU meows]
Ladies and gentlemen,
we would like to thank you
for flying with us today.
In preparation for landing
at Tokyo Narita airport,
please make sure your
seatbelt is securely fastened.
The "Newly Dead" Period.
This period is
followed by a two week span
in which a zombie's emotions,
desires, and instincts
become blurred.
No matter how much rationality
they may seem to possess,
they have the urge to
devour their loved ones.
This is called
the "Confused" period.
Oh, Professor Jojo.
I'm excited to see what kinds of
samples await me here in Japan.