[owls hooting and
crickets chirping]
[footsteps]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
[REA gasps]
[REA screams]
My name is Chihiro Furuya.
I'm a lowly freshman at
Shiyo Prefectural High School.
[ZOMBIE GIRL 1A moans]
[gun cocks]
[gunshot]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
What a waste.
[CHIHIRO] I'm a devotee
of the undead.
I like horror in general
but zombies really speak to me.
[ZOMBIE GIRL 1B moans]
[WOMAN 1A screams]
[CHIHIRO whimpers]
I know this'll sound weird,
but ever since I was a kid
I've dreamed of having
a zombie girlfriend.
[ZOMBIE GIRL 1B] Please.
I don't want to hurt you.
[ZOMBIE GIRL 1B] I didn't
choose to become a zombie.
Deep down,
I'm just a regular girl
who wants to be loved.
[CHIHIRO panting]
[YASUTAKA] You are
one twisted perv, man!
You wanna get it on
with a zombie chick?
I don't remember saying
anything about "getting it on."
Whatever. I think it'd be cool.
How is doin'
a zombie girl cool?
[CHIHIRO] I can't
really explain it.
There's just
something about 'em.
[MOGI] Well, recent
studies suggest that men
are attracted to
vulnerable women;
perhaps that's why he
finds them so appealing.
You think?
We know you're smart;
you don't have to rub
it in, Einstein.
Oh, okay.
The guys just don't get it,
and I can't say I blame 'em.
It's hard to explain.
Especially since I don't really
understand the
attraction myself.
This is Shiryoji Temple.
There's nothing
particularly special about it
except it's my home.
I live here with
my grandpa, Jogoro....
[JOGORO yells]
My old man, Do'on,
the temple priest.
And my kid sister, Mero.
My dad makes breakfast
but other than that,
she does all the housework.
You don't meet many
12 year olds like her.
We are thankful for this meal.
--Yeah, thanks.
--Very thankful indeed.
[JOGORO] Mero dear,
why's there slimy green stuff
floating in my miso soup?
[MERO] Don't freak out, Grandpa.
It's just cabbage.
[JOGORO gags]
I'll be damned.
[CHIHIRO] That's Babu.
He's a stray cat who
became a part of the family
when I found him
wandering the temple grounds.
[BABU meows]
[JOGORO] Mero!
Why's there slimy green stuff
floating in my miso soup?
[MERO] Like I said,
it's cabbage, Grandpa.
[JOGORO gags]
[CHIHIRO] Grandpa's senility
can be stressful,
but our family's pretty happy.
Well, there's one downer.
My mom died when I was little.
I barely even
remember her anymore.
Life is easier when your
memories start to fade.
We still miss her but it gets
a little better every day.
Our family's happy.
At least we were,
until one of us died.
[tires screeching]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
[CHIHIRO yells in agony]
Babu!
[OLD MAN 1A] Chihiro.
I'm so sorry.
He just jumped out
in front of my truck.
I didn't have
time to stop.
[CHIHIRO]
He was hit by an old man
from the neighborhood
who I'd known forever.
It's not like I could
rage at the guy.
So I just cried like a baby.
Babu!
Sorry about this, kids.
We're not allowed
to hold services
for animals
inside the temple.
Personally, I don't mind,
but it might upset
our parishioners.
They just don't understand
what we're going through.
Hey Brother?
[CHIHIRO]
What?
I know as temple children
we're supposed to stay strong,
but would it be okay to cry
at a time like this?
Yeah, we're only human.
True.
[MERO crying]
Babu's death hurt more
than I ever could've imagined.
He wasn't even that old.
He should've had a long
life ahead of him.
But it was taken
from him far too soon.
It wasn't fair.
That's when a crazy idea
popped into my head.
Found it.
I went to visit a relative
in Tohoku last year
and as we were
sorting through stuff
to donate to a local museum,
I came across something amazing.
It wasn't really a book per se,
more like a collection of notes.
It was so beat up I couldn't
even tell when it was written.
The museum's curator told us
it wasn't worth anything,
but after skimming through it
I was sure they were notes
on the reanimation process.
I knew it was probably
a load of bull,
but I figured it couldn't
hurt to give it a try.
I chose an abandoned hotel
as my lab.
I knew nobody would
come looking for me here.
My love of zombies is about
to be put to the test.
What am I gonna do when there's
a real one right in front of me?
I'm gonna bring you
back to life Babu.
Things got weird
on the second day.
[CHIHIRO gasps]
[REA screams]
[alarm ringing]
[CHIHIRO groans sleepily]
[CHIHIRO yawns]
[MERO] Excuse me.
[CHIHIRO gasps]
What exactly
are you doing?ç
Nothing!
Geez, you're like
a freakin' ninja.
That's not a valid
answer to my question.
You can't do "nothing."
Your behavior's been
so suspicious lately.
I'm not doing anything.
That's my story
and I'm stickin' to it.
[door opens and closes]
Oh, he's up
to something.
Just hang in there,
little buddy.
[YASUTAKA]
Earth to Furuya!
Are you even
listening to me, dude?
[CHIHIRO yawns]
Yeah, yeah.
I'm listening.
You know, you're
a terrible liar.
The apathetic look on your
face totally gives you away.
Why would I lie about
something like that?
Fine, then why don't you share
your thoughts on the subject?
[CHIHIRO]
And that was?
[YASUTAKA] I knew
you weren't listening!
I was talking about
how our school's
different from
Sanka Girl's.
Well, I can think of
one glaring difference.
Sanka Academy students
are some of the brightest
and most beautiful
girls in Japan.
Meanwhile, the boys
at our school
are a bunch of
dopey schmucks.
I know they're superior
to us in every way
but why do we have to take
different routes to school?
Maybe cuz Sanka's on the
opposite side of the river?
But they're so far away!
Aaagh!
The only reason I came to Shiyo
was I thought I'd meet a nice
young lady, or two, or three.
How am I gonna meet
the woman of my dreams
when I can't get close
enough to charm 'em!
[CHIHIRO] More like scare 'em.
Hey, have you heard
about the celebrity hottie?
[YASUTAKA chuckles]
You'll wanna swim across
the river when you see her.
Trust me.
Look, there she is!
You see that girl
with the long, black hair?
She's the daughter of the
Sanka Girls' Academy director.
Rea Sanka!
Wow, you guys have no
idea what you're missing.
She's beauty and
elegance personified.
And her family
is stinkin' loaded,
so when we get married
I won't ever to work again!
[CHIHIRO] She's her
own person, ya know.
Oh, Come on!
Don't tell me you wouldn't
wanna follow in your
rich parents' footsteps?
[RANKO] Delivery!
Thanks for swinging by, Ranko.
[DO'ON] I really appreciate it.
Mero's at a school function so
I had to improvise for dinner.
You just say the word
and I'll be right over, Uncle.
It's nice to get a break
from the restaurant and Mom.
[DO'ON laughing]
I bet it is.
It's so quiet.
Where's Chihiro?
[DO'ON sighs]
Probably lying down
in his room again.
Is he okay?
Well, I'm no psychologist but I
get the feeling he's depressed.
I would be too if
I lost my best friend.
Aw, he misses Babu.
Wakey, wakey!
[CHIHIRO grumbles]
What do you
want, "Wanko"?
Oh please,
don't get up.
Here ya go.
Oh right, I forgot
I lent this to you.
That's not the only thing
you forgot, short bus.
You promised you'd
come to my place
over the weekend
to pick it up.
Oh yeah.
[CHIHIRO chuckles]
I'm sorry, I had a busy weekend.
You expect me
to believe that?
You were sittin' here
watching movies alone
when you could've
watched 'em with me!
[CHIHIRO wails]
Hey, can I ask ya
something, Wanko?
That would be miss to you.
Fine, Miss Wanko.
What's up?
Is there a girl at your
school named Rea Sanka?
Well, yeah.
Why do you ask?
I was wondering if she's cool.
I couldn't tell ya.
I don't know know her but
she's the director's daughter
so she's kinda hard to miss.
She's okay I guess.
Why the sudden interest?
Don't tell me you've got the
hots for her, you horndog!
It's not like that!
I was just asking
a simple question!
Yasutaka was making
a big deal about her.
I thought you were in here
sulking 'cause Babu died,
but you're just daydreaming
about some chick!
No, that's not true!
Would you let go of me already?
Okay. Guess I'll
catch you later.
Bye.
You'd better not forget to
come by again this weekend.
Who knows what'll happen.
I might decide to
have my way with you!
[RANKO giggles]
She's insane.
And bring another
zombie movie for me to borrow!
Just take one with you now!
See you this weekend!
Ranko Saoji is my cousin.
She works for her
family's restaurant
and she's a sophomore
at Sanka Academy.
Geez, why does she like playing
the "bossy older sister,"
she's only a few
months older than me.
So he's got a thing
for Rea Sanka...
[wind rustling
and birds chirping]
Uh-oh.
Probably would've been
smart to make a copy first.
The book is incredibly fragile,
and there's a page
that's unreadable.
It's calling for some
kind of poisonous plant,
but its name is
completely blacked out.
I tried using water hemlock
the night before
but that didn't work.
'kay, here's hoping
this one'll do the trick.
I feel bad carrying
Babu around in a cooler.
If I can't get this to
work by the weekend.
I'm gonna bury him.
[footsteps]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
Here we go again.
[REA screams]
[REA panting]
What did I do to deserve this?
I wish I was never born
into the Sanka family!
I just want to
be a normal teenager.
I want to be able
to have friends
and go out like
other girls my age.
It's not fair
you're so overprotective.
I've always been
the perfect daughter
so why can't you trust me?
I'm not a baby anymore.
--I'm in high school!
--[CHIHIRO] Man...
--I'm practically grown!
--The poor girl.
It sounds like her parents
are pretty hard on her.
I follow your rules.
I do everything you tell me.
And I've kept your secret.
Even though it hurts.
I don't care if you're just
trying to commemorate
my growth, Father!
I don't like you taking naked
pictures of me on my birthday!
[REA gasps]
[CHIHIRO] Uhh...
[REA whimpers]
[raining]
[awkward silence]
Now what'll I do?
So... it's really
comin' down, isn't it?
Please!
Don't tell anyone
what you heard!
I'm begging you!
I'll do anything!
Nobody knows.
He'd be so angry.
Promise you won't tell?
Okay, I promise.
But can I talk about the stuff
that I heard last night?
[REA screams]
You heard what I said at
the well yesterday, too?
Yeah. I probably shouldn't
have mentioned that, huh?
I wish I could
just curl up and die.
I'd be better off that way.
Maybe I could come
back as someone else
and live a happy life.
Things at home might be tough
but it's not worth dying over.
I don't wanna sound insensitive
but it's kinda nice
to know you trust fund
kids have it hard, too.
We think
you've got it easy
just because
you're wealthy.
I can only imagine what it's
like to have overbearing parents
constantly shoving rules and
etiquette down your throat.
If I had to deal
with that crap
I bet I'd be out there
screaming my head off with you.
So what brings you here?
Are you trying to escape
your troubles like I am?
Oh no, no,
no, no, no.
[REA] No way! You're bringing
him back from the dead?
That's amazing.
Are you sure it's
going to work?
It hasn't yet
but I'll keep trying.
I don't know what to expect,
but even if he comes
back as a zombie
it's better than not
having him around.
I guess so...
I don't think Babu's
gonna be too jazzed
about joining the
legion of the undead
but I'm hoping he won't
hold it against me.
I know it's selfish but...
I just want my little buddy
to be part of my life again.
It's a win-win situation.
I get Babu
back and he gets...
Now that I think about it,
maybe it'd be better for
both of us if I gave up.
No!
You can't give up
on Babu yet!
I'm sure he'd be
happy to see you!
Even if it meant he
had to become a zombie.
Well, that's one way
to convince me.
I just realized you never
told me your name.
Oh.
It's Chihiro.
I'm Rea.
Nice to meet you.
Don'tcha mean
"nice knowin' ya"?
I didn't think you'd
be sticking around.
Oh... Actually, I was
wondering if it'd be okay
for me to come
back tomorrow.
Huh? You for real?
Why would a proper
lady like you
wanna help out a
nerdy guy like me?
I've always wanted a pet
but my father won't allow it
because he's a germaphobe.
If this works and we bring Babu
back to life,
it'll be the closest I've ever
been to having a furry friend.
Oh, I mean...
He's your cat but I hope
you'll let me play with him.
Well, maybe.
Earlier you said you
would do anything I want.
Remember?
Yeah... I remember.
You wanna play with Babu?
Then prove your loyalty,
by acting as the test
subject for the potion.
You... want me
to drink it?
That's right.
Didn't you say you wanted to die
and come back as someone else?
This is your chance
to become... a zombie.
Ha! I was only kidding!
[REA whimpers]
Man, I had no idea
you were so gullible!
You really shouldn't believe
everything you're
told, princess.
I'm telling you.
Guys can smell
naivety a mile away.
And I know plenty of dudes
who would love to take
advantage of you.
Well how would I know that?
I've never been on...
I, uh...
I've never been on a date with
a boy before.
Well, not yet.
But I don't need protecting!
Quit treating me like
I'm a little girl!
The princess of Sanka Academy's
never had a boyfriend?
I want to, but I can't.
It's my father.
Fine, you win.
All right,
what about you?
What about me?
Uh... well, have you ever
had a girlfriend before?
I haven't met
the right girl.
You don't have any
right to tease me
about never
having a boyfriend
when you've never
had a girlfriend!
I don't want one.
I have no interest in
dating regular girls.
Why's that?
My heart has been stolen by
the beauties of the undead.
What?
I know you think
I'm joking, but I'm not.
They're just the only
ones who do it for me.
I've loved 'em ever since
I was a little boy.
I would totally have
a girlfriend right now
if I could
find a zombie girl.
But they don't exist
so what can ya do?
Call me crazy,
but I refuse to give up hope.
I mean, you
never know, right?
What's the matter?
You feeling inferior?
[REA] Chihiro...
[CHIHIRO] Hmm?
I'll do whatever it takes,
as long as you promise
whenever I become a zombie
you'll take
good care of me.
[CHIHIRO gasps]
Well, uh...
[REA chuckles]
Silly boy.
You really shouldn't believe
everything you're told.
I should head home
before it gets too late.
Goodnight.
Damn, I can't believe she turned
the tables on me like that.
Oh, Chihiro?
Just wanted to say, thanks
again for letting me help you.
See you tomorrow. 'Kay?
[REA giggles]
[CHIHIRO] At that moment,
I never could have imagined...
That the
beautiful girl in front of me?
[REA]
Chihiro... Please...
Help me.
[CHIHIRO] Would eventually
become a zombie.
What?
You want me to
read the preview?
I don't know if that's
such a good idea.
Especially not
with this script.
Would you mind if I
had a quick word
with the writer
before we record?
Oh, we're already
recording?
I see.
Okay then, here goes nothing.
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 2,
"It Was... Successful."
Tune in to see Mero!
I feel like I don't
even know you anymore.