[AIHA]
Dr. Kuga. I need help.
Can I have a bit more
of that medicine?
[KUGAHA] Hm. This one looks
deeper than the last.
What did you do to Tsuguha?
Did you lose control again?
You can't blame me!
Tsuguha's a glory hog!
I fought honorably as
our lady's Divine Garment
for a half-century.
Until that four-eyed loser
showed up and took my spot!
I want to help the
master, that's all!
[KUGAHA]
Actually...
If you're willing, there is
a way you can help her.
Can I count on you, Aiha?
[CLERK 3A]
Thank you! Have a good day.
I better get going.
See you guys tomorr--
[YAMA] Wait just a second.
Why two cheese buns?
You can't be that hungry.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
[AMI] You know, you
have been going off
on your own a lot
lately. Why is that?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Wha--? No, of course not!
Such a vehement denial.
Yep. Suspicious!
Very suspicious!
Well, you'll have to
introduce us to him sometime.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
He'd better be hot!
[HIYORI]
Wait!
[AMI] Give your love
a smooch for us, okay?
Oh, come on. It's not like that!
[HIYORI]
I know that smell.
[YATO grunts]
Why are you always following me?
Huh? Stalker Boy?
I'm not stalking you,
I'm watching you!
It's a totally
legitimate job duty!
[HIYORI]
Nothing better to do, huh?
Giving you divine
protection isn't nothing!
That's blasphemous!
[HIYORI]
Here, take it.
Make sure you give
some to Yukine.
You asked me to get you
a Four-Cheese
Melty Bun, remember?
[sighs]
[HIYORI] I don't know
what's got you acting
like this lately, but it's
really getting out of hand.
Tell you what.
How about I make it a point
to see you every day?
Will that make you feel better?
Maybe then you can stop
sneaking around like a...
[gasps] Hey! Don't get
the wrong idea, okay?
You just still haven't done
the job I paid you to do!
So, I...
[sighs]
Look. Unlike you,
I keep my promises.
And I promise. I'm not
going to forget you!
[HIYORI]
Uh...
I hope that doesn't
turn out to be a lie.
Huh? What's that?
[YATO] Your panties
were showing just then.
Ah!
[yells]
[hisses]
[KAZUMA]
I owe you an apology.
Lady Bishamon has been
in poor health recently.
And in my desperation,
I acted rashly.
[KUGAHA] You haven't heard
the latest news, have you?
Huh?
[KUGAHA]
It seems Suzuha has died.
[KAZUMA gasps]
I also wondered
why Lady Bishamon
had been feeling
so poorly lately.
I checked to see if a
Regalia had gone missing.
Suzuha descended
to the Lower Realm
on a daily basis
to care for his tree.
I can only assume Phantoms
in the area preyed on him.
[KUGAHA] The pain of losing
a Regalia in such a way
must be incredible.
I doubt it is something that you
or I could ever comprehend.
What torment!
For her to suffer alone,
and in silence...
That's her way.
Always so strong.
Could you stay by our lady's
side until I return?
I need to find out more about
what happened to Suzuha.
[groans] My back is
completely destroyed again!
Do you wanna move?
I'm cleaning, here!
[coughs] Would it kill you
to show your master respect
once in a while?
Yeah, it might.
Listen, I was gonna
go see Suzuha
after I'm done
with these chores.
That's cool, right?
No. It's not.
[gasps] What do you mean?
You had no problem
with it the other day.
So what changed?
[YATO] Forget Suzuha. You won't
be seeing him anymore.
Huh?
Yeah, you and
Bishamon have issues,
but that's got nothing to do
with us. Suzuha's my friend.
I don't know what
the big deal is--
[YATO]
Yukine.
Stay away from that cherry tree.
[KUGAHA]
Pardon me, Lady Bishamon.
I've brought your medicine.
Who--? Oh, Kugaha.
[BISHAMON]
I'm a bit dazed. I was dreaming.
[KUGAHA]
Oh? Of what?
Of a boy who loved
to grow flowers,
and the day that I named him.
Never mind. I'm rambling.
I've been feeling so very
weak and run-down lately.
At least I haven't
been corrupted, though.
[KUGAHA]
It's too bad Kazuma isn't here.
I know what a help he is to you.
[BISHAMON]
Yes. He's very busy these days.
[KUGAHA] He just left
for the Lower Realm.
He seemed to be in a hurry.
Oh, really? I wonder
what he's up to.
You wouldn't happen to know?
[KUGAHA]
Well, I don't have any details.
I really shouldn't say.
Oh, what is it?
[KUGAHA] I hate to gossip,
but, I saw something.
I saw Suzuha and the
Yato god's Regalia together.
[KUGAHA] I hope you haven't
burned yourself, my lady!
I'll brew some more
right away. Excuse me.
No, it can't be. Surely.
[panting]
That did it.
I think I finally
ditched my stalker.
Whoops! I dropped
my snack stick!
[YATO]
Oooh!
[YUKINE]
That ought to buy me 45 minutes.
[YATO]
Heaven!
Man, what's his problem, anyway?
All I want is to go see
my friend. He's such a jerk.
I hope Suzuha's around today!
Kazuma's here?
[YATO]
Yukine.
Stay away from that cherry tree.
[YUKINE panting]
It isn't safe there.
Suzuha?
[YATO groans]
Yukine.
Nora.
[NORA giggles] Humans carry
so many emotions with them,
even in death.
Joy. Anger. Heartache. Pleasure.
Look. See how
easily it unravels?
Once a bond has come unraveled,
there's no mending it.
Careful not to become entangled,
or it will choke you
as a Scourge.
You know, Yato.
If something holds you back,
you're better off
just cutting it down.
[KAZUMA] It was faint,
but I could sense a Storm
had been there. Phantoms really
must have attacked him.
I was so focused on Veena,
I forgot about everyone else.
I failed as their exemplar!
[YUKINE]
Kazuma! Wait!
[groans]
[KAZUMA, YUKINE groan]
[REGALIA gasp]
Oww.
Yukine?
Huh? Hey, what happened?
What is this? Where am I?
[KAZUMA]
Are you crazy?
This is Lady Bishamon's manor!
Whoa. Is it, really?
Well, that's perfect!
Suzuha! I know you're here!
--Suzuha!
--[KAZUMA] No! Yukine, stop!
Suzuha is--
He's gone. Suzuha is dead.
He's... dead?
[KAZUMA] Never mind that!
You need to hide!
If Veena should find you here--
[footsteps]
[BISHAMON]
Gaiki!
[gasps]
[REGALIA gasp]
[KURAHA]
No! Milady!
You mustn't shed
blood here! Please.
Well, Kazuma. Do you
care to explain?
What are you doing
with his Regalia?
It's complicated.
Please, I know you hate Yato,
but I'm a friend of Suzuha's.
Suzu...
[YUKINE] Please, Lady
Bishamon, will you tell me
how he died? I want to know
what happened to my friend!
Yukine. He was attacked.
Phantoms got him
in the Lower Realm.
[YUKINE]
What the hell?
I asked you. You're his
master, aren't you?
You named him, didn't you?!
Then why couldn't you
answer me? I get it!
You have so many, what does
one measly Regalia
matter, right?
Don't you care that he's dead?
It hurt him to be ignored,
but I bet you didn't know that!
[SUZUHA] Considering how
many Regalia she has,
I haven't been
called up in years.
[YUKINE]
But he still smiled.
Whatever else he felt,
he kept inside.
He smiled so that
you wouldn't suffer.
Always. Always.
He always, always, always
forced himself to smile.
For decades!
Together, they're the
ultimate team of Regalia
for the ultimate
god of war, Bishamon!
[YUKINE]
Ultimate god, my ass!
You couldn't be bothered
to protect one Regalia,
and now he's dead. Some god!
[SUZUHA] Even with so many,
she treats us like family.
It's just one big,
happy family, huh?
Looks like hell to me.
[cries]
[gasps]
Veena!
[ALL sobbing]
[groans, pants]
Stay calm!
We all must stay in
tune with each other.
[BISHAMON]
Is it true?
There was a rumor about you.
That you helped with an
ablution that saved Yato!
Have you been in contact
with him? Tell me!
Oh, Veena.
He isn't your mortal enemy!
He is your savior!
Huh?
You're wrong!
He is the monster who
slaughtered my family.
How could you do this to me?
You... traitor!
[REGALIA 3A]
He drew a line...
[REGALIA 3B]
...against the master!
Choki!
I, the god Bishamon...
...hereby revoke your--
[BISHAMON]
Consider yourself exiled.
Be a Nora for all I care.
Help the new girl.
It's really sad about
Kazuma getting kicked out,
but I guess I don't get
why it's that big a deal.
I mean, these things
happen, right?
Regalia get fired all the time.
It's not like we
can't replace him.
He was just a navigator.
[KAZUHA]
No. He's not "just a navigator."
What do you mean, Kazuha?
You know Karuha and I
are the lady's guns.
We may be powerful, but we
have a hard time aiming.
Kazuma's the one who
helps us hit our targets.
Without him, we'll actually
be a lot less accurate.
Whoa! Seriously?
That goes for me, too.
Yugiha, no way!
[YUGIHA]
My blade is really sharp.
It can cut almost anything,
but I'm terrible at
drawing Borderlines.
So, I end up cutting things
of the living world, too.
It's Kazuma who
helps hold me back.
With him gone, it'll be
more hit-or-miss.
[TSUGUHA]
Our awesome war god is starting
to sound more like a plain
old god of destruction!
What are we gonna do?
[KUGAHA]
Calm down, everyone.
There's no point moaning
about Kazuma's absence.
We need to stay strong
and believe in ourselves.
[KAZUHA]
You might be right.
First, touch base with
all the other Regalia.
Tell them not to spend
their time dwelling
on Kazuma's betrayal.
Lady Bishamon has enough
heartache as it is.
I don't want any of us
causing her more pain.
I'm lost. So, Kazuma
was working with Yato,
who killed a bunch
of us years ago?
But what exactly
happened back then?
Who were the Regalia he killed?
[KURAHA] No one really
knows the answer to that.
None of us, anyway.
The only ones who
were actually there
when it happened were
Milady and Kazuma.
They speak of it
very rarely. But...
He isn't your mortal enemy!
He is your savior!
What did he mean?
How is Yato her savior?
--[KUGAHA] Stop that.
--[KURAHA] Huh?
Kazuma's a traitor and we
mustn't pay heed to his words.
It's true we have
lost our leader.
but our goal remains the same.
We must gather our strength
and protect our master.
[KAZUHA, KARUHA]
Yes, Dr. Kuga.
[KINUHA] That's the only
thing we can do now.
[DAIKOKU] Oh, good.
Another stray to take in.
I'm sorry. I couldn't think
of anywhere else to go.
We give Yukine
a room to study in,
and this is what happens.
We aren't running a bed
and breakfast here, people.
[YATO]
What's the harm in letting
Yukine's friends sleep over?
Lighten up, Daddy Daikoku!
[growls]
You call me that again
and I will break your face!
This is all your
fault, as usual!
None of it would have
happened if you weren't
so easily distracted
by your stomach!
Eat before it gets cold,
Kazu. Go on, take it.
Waste any and I'll kill you!
It smells delicious.
You're so kind.
I'm sorry. I've been so
worried about Veena.
And the Regalia I let die.
A Regalia? What,
you mean Suzuha?
It isn't like you
killed him, though.
I didn't protect him.
It's close enough.
No, it's not.
Quit blaming yourself
for everything.
That really affects
us, you know!
Yukine's hurting,
First, he loses his friend,
then he gets you in
trouble with your master.
He's taking it hard.
[YATO]
I don't blame him.
It's got me feeling
like crap, too.
Why stay here?
There must be safer
places for you to go.
Aren't you risking
Veena discovering you?
[YATO]
Yeah. I guess I am.
[HIYORI]
No change. He's still crying.
How are you holding up, Yato?
I'm okay.
Hey! You're drinking
at a time like this?
Don't you care about Yukine?
I am pretty sure they say
booze is the best medicine.
You've had enough!
[yells] Wait, give it back!
Please! It helps me!
--You don't understand!
--[HIYORI] Quit pulling on me!
[KAZUMA] Oh, I see. So that's
the reason he stays.
[NORA] Looks like
everything worked out.
[KUGAHA]
Yes.
Yato's kid Regalia showing up
like that was a nice surprise.
He fit into the plan perfectly.
Kazuma didn't get
his name revoked...
But I would bet Bishamon
won't use him again.
So, does that mean it's time?
[HIYORI] You look like
you're in a lot of pain.
[YATO] Yeah. Yukine's been
depressed since it happened.
He won't even get out of bed.
[HIYORI]
How is Kazuma?
[YATO]
Fine, I think.
He's got something on his mind,
but I don't know what.
Poor guy. I wonder
what'll happen to him.
Actually, what about you?
Isn't your big
advancement exam tomorrow?
I've got a great idea!
You should pray to
me you'll pass it!
[sighs]
Well, why not?
It's only five yen.
[wings flap]
Hey. Need help with something?
[HIYORI]
Hm?
I'm one of Bishamon's
Regalia. Aiha.
--[HIYORI gasps]
--[YATO] A scourged staff.
Not the kind of weapon
you see every day.
Your master gives you
some dangerous toys.
[AIHA] Be quiet! You are
my master's sworn enemy.
Everything I do here is for her!
Get away!
Yato! Are you okay?
[YATO] Damn you, Bishamon!
Sending a Regalia!
Did you lose it after
throwing Kazuma out?
[gasps]
Let me help you out with this.
[YATO]
What the--? Hiyori!
Really? Again!
Hey! Stop! This is my fight!
[yelps]
There, you see?
She's been given a weapon.
This is nothing like
fighting a Phantom!
You let me handle this.
But you're not feeling so well,
and Yukine isn't here.
I can't use my Sekki now.
That's probably
why she attacked.
[YATO]
Guess I'll ask.
Hey!
You wouldn't kill
me! I'm a girl!
[YATO]
Like I care.
Women and children are
nothing special to a god.
Did you wait until
I was alone to strike?
Did you think I would
be helpless unarmed?
And the way you looked at me.
You really hate me, don't you?
You've heard all about how
I killed your comrades--
Stop!
[HIYORI]
Yato! Don't follow--
[AIHA, YATO panting]
[YATO]
A Phantom?
[YATO grunts]
[SPIDER PHANTOM 3A]
Smells nice.
Great. Just what I need.
[SPIDER PHANTOMS]
Smells nice... Smells nice...
There are so many of them!
Where'd they come from?
An ambush! Damn!
[HIYORI grunts]
[HIYORI whimpering]
[clapping]
[KUGAHA]
All right. That's enough.
Hiyori. Hi there.
How are you today?
[HIYORI]
Those are Phantoms!
[AIHA panting]
Dr. Kuga! Hurry!
[KUGAHA]
Yes, yes. I'm coming.
All this effort will be for
nothing should Yato return.
[KAZUMA]
Kugaha! Aiha!
[gasps]
Restraint!
Ah! I'm glad to see you!
Are you okay?
Yes, but what are
you doing here?
I still had some
questions about Suzuha.
So I came looking for Yato.
I never expected to find this!
Where did you get this?
Scourges corrode Regalia!
[KAZUMA] You've used the
names your master gave you
to employ Phantoms and interfere
with the living world!
Do you even realize
how demeaning this is
to our master? A name is proof
of a Regalia's humanity!
No! Restraint!
[KAZUMA]
Kugaha! Restraint!
You can't move!
Not when I've
restrained your name!
I was disappointed when
she didn't get rid
of you entirely, but now I
see it's worked in my favor.
Because if you were nameless,
you would be immune
to my invocations.
Kazuma. Slumber.
[YATO panting]
[KUGAHA] What are you going
to do about this, Yato?
Hey! Wake up!
[KUGAHA]
The human you cherish so much
has been taken from
you by Bishamon.
[DAIKOKU] Organic daikon,
dye-free mouthwash,
all-natural shampoo... Huh?
What are you
grinning for, Kofuku?
[KOFUKU] It's so sweet
of you to do Kazu's
shopping for him, Daikoku!
On the next Noragami
Aragoto: "Wish."
[DAIKOKU]
That's it! No more freeloaders!