Ready. Go!
[HIYORI]
Ready... Go!
No use. It won't work.
[HIYORI panting]
[sighs]
Easy. Are you okay?
[HIYORI]
Yeah. I'm just a little tired.
[KAZUMA gasps]
[KAZUMA]
Her Cord is starting to fade.
Being here in her ethereal
form is dangerous.
If we don't lift
the Scourge soon,
her physical body will die.
This is my fault.
I played right into
Kugaha's hands.
Before long, he'll have won.
Please, Veena.
[yelling]
[YATO grunts]
[YATO]
Tch! Nice try! Sekki!
Now!
[KINUHA, KURAHA, AKIHA]
Confine!
[gasps]
[BISHAMON]
You're finished.
Come, Saiki!
[BISHAMON grunts]
[YATO]
No--
Yukine!
[YATO grunts]
[YATO coughs]
Hard to believe he
sacrificed himself
to protect you.
Maybe now you
understand the agony
of losing a Regalia.
[BISHAMON]
I'll put you out of your misery.
[YATO]
Yukine! Yukine!
[gasps]
[YATO]
His name. It's still there!
Sekki!
[gasps]
[BISHAMON grunts]
That light. What is this?
Impossible...
This is what
happened with Kazuma.
He wasn't much as a new Regalia.
Just a small nail.
[BISHAMON]
But rarely, very rarely,
a Regalia will transform.
It happens only
with the most sincere
and loyal of them.
The Blessed Vessels!
Wow. That was pretty
amazing. Are you okay?
I'm not sure how,
but I think I am.
Everything happened so fast.
I guess I got carried away.
Before I knew it, I'd
turned into two blades.
[YATO]
Thank you, Yukine.
Huh?
As long as I've lived,
you're the first Regalia
to change for me.
I'm so gonna brag to
everybody about this.
Brag? You mean, about me?
[BISHAMON growls]
A god of calamity
with a Blessed Vessel?
[gasps]
[gasps] Her sword
didn't break me!
[YATO]
Yeah! You're awesome, kid!
[yells]
What do you say? You ready
to get Hiyori back?
Let's do it!
[AIHA]
My lady!
[KUGAHA] Heh. I didn't expect
that brat to evolve
at the last second.
This is perfect.
Stop! You let go of me!
That medicine should
be wearing off.
[PHANTOM 3A cackles]
[groans]
[grunting]
[YATO grunts]
[yells]
[gasps]
[BISHAMON yells]
[yelling]
What's happened to her?
Don't tell me...
I can't believe it.
Our lady's been corrupted!
No, this can't be happening!
[YATO]
Tch! Not again!
I don't think so!
You're staying right
where you are.
No, stay back!
I don't want you blighted, too!
Are you really surprised
you've been tainted?
You did arm a Regalia.
And kidnap an innocent!
Let's end this!
Give Hiyori back now!
We would never do the
things you're suggesting!
[YATO] Then how do you
explain the blight?
[YATO] She got like this because
one of you tainted her.
Badly.
Yes. He's right. But who is it?
Time for another round
of the blame game.
I think you know
how it's played.
[BISHAMON]
Kinki!
[KURAHA] Milady, I'll take
you away from here!
[BISHAMON]
Attack him.
[KURAHA]
Huh?
If we want to save everyone,
we have to kill Yato!
[KURAHA, KINUHA, AKIHA gasp]
That's one crazy chick.
[KUGAHA laughs] Have you seen
the shape Bishamon's in?
It's only a matter of time now
until Yato finishes her off.
And while he's at it,
maybe he can get rid
of her whole
entourage for me, too.
What an idiot Kazuma is.
Honestly, he's as
blind as they get.
He couldn't see that
something had to be done.
Fortunately, I was
willing to step in.
Soon, Bishamon will be
reincarnated, and then...
...I'll be the exemplar.
Why?
Why would you do this to her?
[KUGAHA]
It's simple.
Our master's a failure.
Her time is up.
[YATO grunts]
[REGALIAS screaming]
[KUGAHA] Like an idiot,
she insists on helping
every pathetic spirit. And then
pats herself on the back
for being so kind and motherly.
[FUMIHA whimpers]
[MINEHA]
My Lady!
[KUGAHA] She's ended up
with a pile of junk Regalia,
all pretending to be
one big, happy family.
That's the mighty Bishamon?
[BISHAMON yells]
[KUGAHA] She's not my master,
I'll tell you that.
Now, stop crying.
There's no need for you
to suffer on behalf
of a wretch like
her. I told you.
Be patient until
after the reincarnation.
[grunts]
[KUGAHA] The next Bishamon won't
scorn you like this one has.
And as the new exemplar,
I'll have the power
to absolve you of guilt.
[YATO yells]
[BISHAMON grunting]
[YATO grunts]
[yelps]
[YATO]
Hey! No! Wait!
[BISHAMON grunts]
[groans]
I'm not gonna let you hurt Yato!
That's my boy!
[yells]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[gasping, panting]
[BISHAMON grunts]
[KURAHA] Milady! Your
blight is worsening!
I'm begging you, please stop!
[yells]
Where is Kazuma?
He's the one we
really need right now.
[KURAHA] Aki! Okinu!
Take everyone inside.
We can't lose ourselves
in this chaos.
Have anyone who can
do so draw a borderline.
--[KINUHA] Right!
--[AKIHA] Yes, sir!
Come on, everybody! This way!
[KURAHA] There has to be
something else I can do.
How do I make sure
we all live through this?
[thud]
[panting]
[KARUHA]
Someone help.
I'm burning up.
Please. Please, my lady!
We can't endure this pain.
Just release us.
[YUGIHA groaning]
Please do it. Release me!
[yells]
[grunts]
[YATO] Even corrupted,
you can still fight?
You may be crazy,
but you're damn tough.
Come, Jinki!
[gasps]
Okinu!
[KINUHA screams]
You're beyond saving now.
[REGALIA 5A]
Run!
[REGALIA 5B]
Everyone into the hall! Hurry!
[groans]
Oh, it's you, Doctor!
Don't look like that.
It's your lucky day.
You second-string Regalia are
finally going to be useful.
[growling]
[REGALIA 5A]
Doctor. Why?
Now we're almost there.
[KAZUMA grunts]
[panting]
[KAZUMA grunting]
[grunts] Damn it!
[gasps]
[gasps] Aiha?
Please. Please forgive me.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
[AIHA grunts, whimpers]
[AIHA] I'm the one who
tainted our master!
You have to stop Dr. Kuga!
If you don't,
everyone's going to die.
What? Everybody?
[KURAHA]
Kazuma!
[gasps]
[KURAHA]
What she says is true.
Our master has been corrupted!
No one knows what to do.
All hell broke loose
after Yato showed up.
If we don't act quickly,
I don't know what could happen.
I'm coming, Veena.
Aiha, we'll talk later.
All right, let's go.
[KURAHA]
Please, get on.
[HIYORI]
Me, too! You said Yato's here.
You need to return
to your body at once!
The Scourge is gone, but you're
still in critical condition.
[HIYORI]
Please, Kazuma. Do this for me.
Take me with you!
[KAZUMA]
No! You're being foolish.
I will not let you die this way!
Now, return immediately!
[HIYORI]
No! You have to take me!
I'm the one who can stop Yato.
[KAZUMA]
I knew it.
He's doing this to
force a reincarnation.
[KURAHA]
So it would seem.
Apparently, he used some
sort of medicine to conceal
the blight until
the opportune moment.
I apologize.
You were right to be suspicious.
What a fool I was.
I blindly trusted him because
he was our master's curer.
I was an idiot not
to see through his ruse.
[KAZUMA] Choosing trust is
usually the best course.
We Regalia cannot afford
to mistrust one another.
Such discord is
toxic to our master.
In extreme cases,
it can even be fatal.
No matter what, we must
continue to smile.
For our Lady's sake.
That's what I've always
taught our family.
Always. But now we
have disgraced her.
Once again.
[HIYORI] Umm. Are you
sure that really helps?
Seems like it must be tough.
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
It sounds like
Bishamon handles things
a lot differently than Yato.
He has no trouble complaining
whenever he's in pain.
And Yukine's not
usually shy about
sharing his feelings, either.
That can lead to a
whole lot of bickering,
but I like that about them.
It's sweet.
You can tell they're actually
close to each other.
More family than friends.
But Bishamon and her Regalia
are quietly suffering
to keep up appearances.
Isn't that sort of
hard on everyone?
[REGALIA screaming]
[SKELETON PHANTOM 2A roaring]
[REGALIA 5C]
A Phantom!
[REGALIA 5D]
What's it doing here?
Masked Ones are a far cry
from ordinary Phantoms.
Your Borderlines won't
last a second against one.
[KUGAHA]
A hearty appetite!
I wonder how much
agony Bishamon is in
after losing so many Regalia.
More to go! So many more!
Find the rest of the survivors,
my Phantom friend.
Hunt them down
and kill them all!
It's headed this way.
We should get out of here.
What are you waiting for?
We need to go now!
[FUMIHA]
Why bother?
[MINEHA]
Huh?
[BISHAMON]
More names have disappeared.
My Regalia are dying.
[REGALIA screaming]
[BISHAMON] This can't
be happening. Not again.
My lady! Help!
Please, my lady!
[BISHAMON]
They're dying again!
[YATO yells]
[BISHAMON]
He's taking them from me again.
Damn you!
[screaming]
[YATO] She's using her Regalia
even after being corrupted?
What the hell is she thinking?
[NORA] You're better off
just cutting it down.
[YATO gasps]
Yato?
[NORA]
Once a bond has come unraveled,
there's no mending it.
[BISHAMON grunts]
[NORA]
Careful not to become entangled,
or it will choke
you as a Scourge.
Yato, look out!
[BISHAMON grunts]
You're better off
just cutting it down.
[HIYORI]
Yato!
Hey. I know that voice.
[HIYORI]
Yato! Stop fighting her!
Veena! It's worse
than I thought.
It's really her. Hiyori's okay!
Look, Yato, do you see her?
Hiyori's here! She's fine!
Bishamon's not who you want!
You were tricked. She's not
the one who kidnapped me!
It was our curer.
Kugaha wanted you to kill Veena.
If you did, she
would reincarnate.
That's what he's after.
[HIYORI] So you can stop
fighting now, okay?
[KAZUMA]
I'm sorry, Veena!
I should have
realized it sooner.
[gasps]
[BISHAMON yells]
Veena!
Sorry, Hiyori.
The fight's not over.
[BISHAMON] Give them back.
Give me my children back!
So I'm still the bad
guy here, is that it?
I get it. That's what kept
you going all this time.
That unjustified hatred.
Whatever. That's fine.
I'm just a filthy Nora-keeper.
So let me do what I do best.
Your Regalia clearly need
killing. I'll do the honors.
[YATO grunts]
[HIYORI]
Yato!
[YATO, BISHAMON grunting]
[KURAHA] What do we do?
We can't just stand here.
Kazuma!
[KUGAHA]
Now, then.
If you'll excuse me,
I have another appointment.
Your dear master
is about to die.
And that is something
I would like to see.
[KURAHA]
Milady!
Yato!
No, stay back!
[YATO] Pretty soon, she's
gonna take us down with her.
We have to kill her.
[gasps]
[YATO]
Don't worry.
She'll be reborn,
and you won't really
be the one doing
the killing, anyway.
This one's all on me.
[YATO] It's okay, kid.
Killing a god's no big deal.
[HIYORI whimpers]
[BISHAMON gasps]
[screams]
[gasps]
[BISHAMON gasps]
[YATO grunts]
[KAZUMA]
Veena. Listen to me.
There's something...
I've never told you.
The Ma Clan's death
wasn't Yato's fault.
It was mine.
I asked him to do it.
[KAZUMA] I betrayed them.
They died and I survived.
I wanted so badly
to tell you the truth.
[KAZUMA]
I can't protect you, master.
I'm just a little nail.
Please, you must find other
Regalia to serve you.
Better ones.
[BISHAMON] No. I never wanna
go through that again.
I don't need
any other Regalia!
All I need is you!
[KAZUMA] In the end,
I wasn't able to say it.
Nor could I stop you
from hating Yato.
You needed that hatred.
It's what gave you new strength.
So you see, I'm a coward!
I only wanted to be with you.
Your words that day were bitter,
but they filled me with
joy. I reveled in it.
And now...
I've made you weep yet again.
Blessed Vessel? That isn't
a title I deserve.
I've failed you in every way.
Just look at us now.
This is where my
guidance has led us.
I've put you through
such anguish.
I don't deserve your
forgiveness, but I am sorry.
[BISHAMON groans]
[sobs]
Oh, Milady.
[sighs]
[HIYORI]
So much pain.
She must have been holding
this in for years...
For centuries. She's
sobbing like a child.
It's done, Bishamon.
Time to end this.
You have to let your Regalia go.
Yugi.
[BISHAMON]
Kinu. Tsugu. Kazu. Karu. Kura.
Kazuma. I'm sorry. So sorry.
It's happened again.
How many members
of my family are dead?
I don't know if I can bear this!
I don't get it.
Yato hasn't killed
anybody tonight.
So who did kill them?
The mastermind of
this little scheme.
[YATO] I can't believe you're
a Blessed Vessel now!
Let's have a party to celebrate.
We'll dress all in white,
buy a huge cake,
and throw rice at each other!
[YUKINE] Uh, no. You're
thinking of a wedding!
[YATO]
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"What Must be Done."
[YUKINE]
I'm not marrying you, dude!