[REGALIAS screaming]
Ah!
[BISHAMON grunts]
Stop.
[REGALIA 1A screams]
[BISHAMON]
Stop. Please don't kill them.
My lady! Help!
Please, my lady!
[REGALIAS]
Lady Bishamoan!
No!
[BISHAMON gasps]
[gasps]
[pants]
[coughs]
[sighs]
Yato.
[phone rings]
[YATO] Hello there,
and thank you for calling!
Fast and affordable, Delivery
God Yato at your service!
[YUKINE]
Damn. It keeps slipping.
Yes, of course!
I'd be more than happy
to accept the job!
I can't do these
handwritten fliers, Yato--
Right!
[screams]
Put down the pen.
We've got work!
[HIYORI humming]
There!
[HIYORI'S MOM]
Hiyori! Breakfast is ready!
I'm coming!
Good morning, Mom.
Good morning, Dad.
Did you sleep well?
Not too bad.
Yes, thank you, dear.
Now, come eat.
I opened that jam we got
as a year-end gift.
Oh, yummy!
I hear that you did well
on your practice exam.
[laughs]
[HIYORI'S MOM] The actual exam
is what matters, though.
You wouldn't wanna
be held back a grade!
[HIYORI]
See you later!
[HIYORI'S MOM]
There's no need to run!
[SASAKI]
Hello there, Hiyori!
[HIYORI]
Oh, good morning, Miss Sasaki.
[SASAKI]
Have a good day!
Morning! Staying warm?
I'm trying, Ami.
Hey, where's Yama?
She headed in early,
the poor thing.
Sounds like she bombed
the practice exam.
Oh, really?
Hey, Yama!
[YAMA]
Yori! Perfect timing!
[HIYORI]
Why's that?
[YAMA] Do you know
the answer to this one?
[HIYORI]
Oh, this is a hard one.
Let's see. If I
remember right...
Thank you.
With your help, maybe
I'll actually pass.
You can teach me everything
I need to know.
My secret weapon!
Be careful, though.
Trying to learn too much, too
quickly, can backfire on you.
Yeah, you're right.
With my luck I'd cram all
night only to fall asleep
during the exam the next day!
Uh, Hiyori?
Huh?
Ah-ha! Hiyori's patented
Insta-Snooze trick!
[AMI] Man, I really hope she
doesn't do this during the test.
[YAMA]
Rise and shine, Hiyori!
Great. Looks like my
soul slipped out again.
Oh, well. What do you
say we go for a walk?
[HIYORI giggling]
[HIYORI]
Smells nice. Is that...?
[cooing]
[YATO]
Have you prepared yourself?
Because the time has come.
Here we go! Almost there! And...
Clean baby!
Oh, wow.
You mean you actually know
how to change diapers?
That was nothing compared to
changing a cloth diaper.
Are you that surprised, though?
I've been around for
a long time, you know.
Who'd let you near their baby?
[HIYORI]
Hey guys! Can I come in?
[YATO]
Hiyori!
I'm not interrupting, am I?
[YUKINE] You sure slip out
of your body a lot.
[YATO]
How'd you know where to find us?
[HIYORI giggles] You doing
some Delivery God work?
Yeah. Yato the babysitter
god, at your service.
I guess his parents
are sleep deprived
because he cries all the time.
Really? He's not crying now.
He seems perfectly happy.
For the moment, sure.
[HIYORI]
Where's his mom, anyway?
[YATO]
Snoring it up in the other room.
Can't blame her. She hasn't
gotten any sleep in a week.
[BABY 1A giggles]
Hey, he's laughing!
He's looking your direction.
I guess he can see you.
[YATO] Actually, it's pretty
normal for animals
and young children
to perceive those of us
from the Far Shore.
[BABY 1A cooing]
[YUKINE]
His skin's so soft.
[HIYORI giggles]
He likes you.
I think he's asking
you to pick him up.
[YUKINE]
Huh?
Uh-- Oh! He's heavy!
And why's he squirming?
It's freaky!
[YATO] Here. Put your
left hand on his back.
Support his head and neck
with your whole arm,
and put your right
hand underneath.
[YUKINE]
O-O-Okay. Like this?
[HIYORI giggles]
[chuckles]
[BABY 1A whines]
[YUKINE] What did I do wrong?
Why is he crying?
[BABY 1A crying]
Huh?
[gasps]
[HIYORI grunts]
[rattling]
[BABY 1A whines]
[HIYORI gasps]
[growls]
We have company!
A Phantom?
[growls]
[HIYORI gasps]
[HIYORI]
Let's go! Jungle Savate!
[YATO] Nice one! Hiyori,
keep an eye on the kid for me.
Huh?
Come, Sekki!
[yelps]
[growling]
Ready, Yukine?
What? No!
[grunts]
You're sharper than I realized!
[YUKINE] Wait a second!
The room's too cramped.
Don't forget,
there's a baby in here!
[YATO] I commend you
for being concerned.
We must take care not
to cause undue harm
to those of this world.
You'll need to hold back.
[YUKINE]
Great. How do I do that?
[YATO]
Let's review, shall we?
[gasps]
[YATO]
You draw a Borderline.
A line between what gets
killed and what survives.
What, or who, I kill is
up to you. Understand?
Yeah, I think so.
This Phantom is
acting really weird!
[YATO]
It's... healing itself?
[BABY 1A whines]
[BABY 1A]
[YATO]
The kid's doing it.
But how?
[YATO] The mirror. This
Phantom is just an image.
One created by the kid himself.
See what he's doing?
He probably wanted
somebody to play with.
So he kept reaching out to his
own reflection in the mirror.
The longing and vulnerability
that poured out of him
summoned a Phantom.
Unless we do
something to stop it,
it will eventually possess his
mother, stealing her humanity.
That's awful!
[YATO] I have to say,
this thought energy
seems unusually
strong for a baby.
Okay, then. What do we do?
[YATO grunts] We slay the real
one-- The one in the mirror.
Keep the baby there, Hiyori.
He needs to see his reflection.
'Kay. Got it.
[growling]
This is the land
of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki,
and expel thy vast
defilement! I cleanse thee!
Rend!
That was incredible, Yukine!
That's my Regalia for ya!
See, I knew you could do it.
[YATO]
He should be safe now.
[HIYORI]
Well, that's a relief.
But... What do we
do about all this?
We scram, obviously.
[YUKINE, HIYORI]
Huh?!
--[HIYORI] That's horrible Yato!
--[YUKINE] I can't believe you!
[HIYORI] Especially when
you're supposed to be
setting a good
example for Yukine.
[YATO]
A mask?
[KAZUMA] You called
for me, Lady Bishamoan?
Yes I did, Kazuma.
Please, come in.
[KAZUMA]
How may I help?
[BISHAMON] How much time
do we have remaining
until our next patrol?
It's today.
We have it planned
for the Fiendish Hour.
[BISHAMON]
I see. It's almost time then.
[KAZUMA]
Is something troubling you?
Well, as a matter of fact,
I had an old nightmare
this morning.
Clashing with Yato again
after all these years
may be to blame.
I'm sorry to hear it.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm quite fine.
However, I'll need you
to locate him again for me.
I must know if we've
overlooked anything.
[KAZUMA] Right. Shall I inform
the curer, to be safe?
Yes.
[KOFUKU]
What? No way!
[HIYORI]
It's true.
But... I'm sure you cleaned up
in the end though, right?
Of course! I insisted.
We couldn't leave it like that!
[YATO] You can guess who she
made do all the cleaning!
[DAIKOKU]
Must've been terrible.
[screams]
Show some respect
for the working class!
You can start by feeding me.
I think I'll have
grilled eel today.
You don't place orders.
You'll take whatever I
give you, and you'll like it!
[YATO] Ah! I think
you punctured a lung!
[HIYORI] Here, Yukine.
You'll need to do this over.
And check your work using
a dictionary this time, okay?
Uh-- Okay.
You're such a strict teacher!
Really? Am I?
How's he doing, anyway?
Does Yukine have
some book smarts?
It kinda varies.
He's better at some
subjects than others.
Overall, I'd say he's
an eighth grader.
[HIYORI] Wait! Eighth grade
is only one below me!
Oh, jeez. What
about that time--?
[HIYORI] It's been a while
since I slept with someone...
[HIYORI]
Uh-oh!
Maybe he thought I meant
slept, slept with someone!
[YUKINE]
What? Is something the matter?
Oh, no. Nothing!
Everything's fine.
It's just dandy.
Nothing's wrong at all!
Heh. You try to act mature,
but you're still young
in so many ways.
Good thing I'm here.
Somebody has to look
out for you two.
You should be thankful.
I may not be a big deal now,
but just you wait!
Before much longer, the whole
world will know my name!
Yeah! I'll have my own
shrine and everything!
Yeah, I dunno.
You've been saying that for
over a century now, Yatty.
You're skeptical. I get that.
But it's different this time.
'Cause now, I have this!
I give. What's it do?
A miraculous lucky cat
made of magic gemstone!
Its beckoning power
is guaranteed
to draw people to the bearer.
It was given to me by
one Master Ishizaki,
a fortuneteller who
once appeared on TV.
The bottom says it's
"made of plastic."
Huh?
[HIYORI]
And it's not beckoning.
Look at the paws.
It's doing a "hurrah" pose.
[YATO]
What?
Talk about a gullible consumer.
[YUKINE] How much did that
fortuneteller charge you?
Two hundred thousand.
Wha--?!
How could you blow
that much money?
[YUKINE]
That kind of cash...
[YATO] Wait! Please!
I bought it for us!
If my luck improves,
so does yours!
Poor Yukki.
It must be rough
being Yatty's Regalia.
Yup.
[YATO screams]
My spleen! You got my spleen--
[HIYORI] Aren't you supposed
to be putting your money
towards a shrine, Yato?
[YATO]
Anyone need the Delivery God?
God-like powers,
at your service!
--[YUKINE] Ah, jeeze.
--Any job--mildew scrubbing,
diaper changing.
Even Phantom slaying.
Any job at all, just five yen!
[YUKINE]
Yato. Look.
[YATO]
Huh?
There's a Storm brewing.
[gasps]
[yelps]
--Hey! What was that f--
--[YATO] Shh!
Hey, that's Bishamon. Right?
Whew. that was a close one.
We would be in for a world
of hurt if she saw us.
Let's just go this way.
[YUKINE]
So, I've kinda been wondering.
How long do we have
to keep avoiding her?
Huh?
[YUKINE] I mean, I owe
Kazuma for helping me
with the ablution.
I'd like to talk
to him and, you know,
maybe say thank yo--
[YATO]
Yukine.
You will stay away
from Bishamon.
[GIRL panting]
Help me! Someone please help!
[GIRL yelps]
[roars]
[BISHAMON] A spirit!
It's being eaten by Phantoms.
Kuraha. Let's go!
[KAZUMA]
Please wait a moment.
[BISHAMON]
What is it now?
You mean to save another spirit?
[BISHAMON]
Of course I do.
We failed to save
her life before.
If I fail her again,
what kind of god am I?
[KURAHA roars]
[screaming]
[KAZUMA]
Best to target the wings.
Gaiki!
Fire!
[BIRD PHANTOMS roar]
Jinki!
[GIRL gasps]
Atop northwest building.
Distance: 31!
[KURAHA roars]
Suki!
[BIRD PHANTOMS groan]
Do it now!
[BISHAMON]
Saiki!
This is the land
of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me, I am the god, Bishamon.
I now lay thee waste
with the Saiki,
and expel thy vast
defilement! I cleanse thee!
Ruin!
[BISHAMON]
Revert, Yugi.
She and Kazuma are
such a perfect team!
Another stellar performance
from the mightiest war god.
[BISHAMON]
Shuki.
This will hurt a bit.
[gasps]
Okay, let's make this quick.
[KAZUMA] Adhesion between
the left biceps, brachii,
and both shoulder blades.
Try to avoid tendon damage.
[screams]
Endure.
There is only one way to remove
Phantom blight from a spirit.
And that's to cut it out.
There. That should be all of it.
[GIRL whimpering]
Spirit, you are lost and adrift.
You have nowhere to go
and nowhere to return to.
Thus, I grant you
a place to belong.
My name is Bishamon.
Bearing two names,
you shall remain here.
With these names,
I make thee my servant.
With these names, I use my life
to make thee a Regalia,
fit to be wielded by a god.
Thou art Mine!
As Regalia, Ryoki! Come, Ryoki!
I don't understand.
Why is she a broken mirror?
Once it has been torn,
the unfortunate spirit
cannot become a proper Regalia.
[TSUGUHA]
Oh.
[KINUHA] That's part of
the reason she goes
out of her way to save them.
[TSUGUHA]
Wow. She's such a kind god.
[BIRD PHANTOM 1J roars]
Look out, my lady!
[KURAHA roars]
[BISHAMON]
Whenever you're ready.
[YUKINE]
I'm so sick of Yato's crap.
Always giving orders
without bothering
to listen to me or
ask how I feel. Ugh.
[STUDENT 1A]
No way! Are you serious?
[STUDENT 1B]
Yeah!
Come by my place if
you don't believe me.
[STUDENT 1A]
Okay, I will!
[STUDENT 1B] I'm telling you,
man, this game is killer.
[YUKINE sighs]
[SUZUHA]
Hey.
Hey. Don't ignore me, kid.
Huh?
Find someplace else to sit.
You're smashing the flowers.
Huh? U-Uh? Hold on a second.
Are you talking to me?
Who else would
I be talking to?
But, that means you
can see me, though.
How is that even possible?
You're a Regalia,
like me, aren't you?
Oh.
Small world, huh?
[BISHAMON]
Revert, Mine.
[MINEHA]
W-Where are we?
[KAZUMA]
You're in Takamagahara.
This is Lady Bishamon's manner.
[BISHAMON] And as of today,
this is where you live, as well.
Huh?
You are part of the
family now. Welcome home.
[REGALIAS laugh, cheer]
[BISHAMON]
From this day forward, Mineha,
you're one of us. I expect
everyone to treat her warmly.
[REGALIAS]
Yes, Lady Bishamon!
[whimpers]
Perhaps we ought
to have somebody
give you a little tour
of the manor. Anybody?
[TSUGUHA]
Sure! I'll do it.
Tsuguha.
I'm still new enough
that getting the chance
to explore the manor
is fun for me.
[BISHAMON]
I see. Well, thank you.
[TSUGUHA]
Let's go!
[BISHAMON sighs]
[KAZUMA]
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
This is all part
of being a master.
Regalia are former humans.
Although their flesh is gone,
their spirits remain.
Fear, suspicion,
envy, resentment.
They feel all these things.
And the pain of a Regalia
with a clouded mind is
also borne by its master.
You mean you've been stung?
I believe I told you
not to worry about me,
didn't I?
Let me worry a little, at least.
You have so many Regalia--
maybe it's time to slow down.
With each new
weapon you take on,
you endanger your
health that much more.
[BISHAMON]
Anyway, moving on.
What news is there on Yato?
Uh.
[BISHAMON]
Have you found him?
[KAZUMA]
No, not yet.
He's a god of calamity.
I can't let him live.
Yuck.
It's very bitter.
You should take it more slowly.
[knocking]
Enter.
Yes, Kugaha?
[KUGAHA] I've readied your
ritual bath, my lady.
[BISHAMON]
I appreciate it.
[KAZUMA]
If you will excuse me, then.
[sighs]
[KUGAHA]
You're looking quite pale today.
Shall I prepare
a medicinal bath?
[BISHAMON]
Please.
[KUGAHA]
Lady Bishamon.
[BISHAMON]
What is it?
[KUGAHA] I've heard a rumor
that I find rather troubling.
Some time back,
Kazuma left the manor
following a meeting
without informing
anyone he was doing so.
Perhaps you recall the occasion?
Yes. I do remember
that happening.
[KUGAHA]
The rumor I spoke of concerns
where he went that day.
[KUGAHA]
An ablution ritual.
That was apparently held
by the calamity god, Yato.
[laughs] Absurd.
Yes, of course it is.
What a ridiculous idea.
[KOFUKU]
Uh-huh. Yeah, sure. Okay!
I'll let him know
for you. Hey, Yatty!
That was Yukki calling.
He says he'll be
back a little late.
Huh?
That darn kid is always
goin' off someplace.
And it's not very long
before dark, either.
[HIYORI]
Yato.
Could you do me a favor
and give this homework
to Yukine for me?
I've labeled a few assignments
he still needs to do.
Sure, but does that
mean you're leaving?
Yes. I need to get home.
I've still got some prep
to do for tomorrow.
So, uh, Hiyori.
Have you seen those new
Four-Cheese Melty Buns
by any chance? They sure
look tasty, don't they?
--Huh?
--[YATO] Mm-mm!
They're the kind of
thing you have to try
before they're gone forever.
You know what I'm talking about!
Yeah. I'll look into it for you.
Cheese bun, score!
You haven't forgotten
what you're
supposed to be doing
for me, have you?
Huh?
I hired you to fix that
little issue I'm having.
You know, how my soul
slips out of my body!
You said you'd take
care of it, remember?
You even took my five-yen coin!
[YATO] Oh, yeah. I'm on it!
Totally! No worries.
[HIYORI]
You made me a promise, Yato!
You'd better find
a way to fix me.
I'm sticking with
you till you do.
[gasps]
[HIYORI]
Well, see you tomorrow!
Tomorrow, then.
[YUKINE, SUZUHA laughing]
Your name's cool. I like it.
Yeah? Thanks.
So, whose Regalia
are you, anyway?
His name's Yato.
He wears a tracksuit.
Yato, huh? Never heard of him.
He's such a minor god,
he might as well not exist.
And you?
Me?
Not bragging or anything,
but my god is totally major.
[YUKINE]
Yeah?
[SUZUHA] I serve one of
the Seven Gods of Fortune.
I'm Lady Bishamon's Regalia!
Ah--
Wow. Seriously?
Seriously!
[YATO]
Ya-ho! It's me, Yato!
A soon-to-be major god and
a snappy high school senior!
[HIYORI]
You? In high school?
[YATO] The tracksuit won't
be weird if I'm a student.
[HIYORI]
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"One of Her Memories."
[YUKINE]
That's not the only
weird thing about you, y'know.