[GODS murmuring]
[GOD 7A] It was always odd
how often he reincarnated,
but this is simply shocking!
[GOD 7B] To think that
Ebisu is the conjurer
that they've been hunting.
[GOD 7D] I hear that he controls
some formidable Phantoms.
[GOD 7A] And did you know
that most of his Regalia
were actually Noras?
[GOD 7B] A God of Fortune,
a Nora-keeping conjurer?
It's practically unthinkable!
[GOD 7A] I wonder why he would
ever do something like this.
That is entirely irrelevant.
Taboos are taboos.
The heavens' disorder begets
humans' disorder.
Time is of the essence.
Ebisu has been
revealed as a Phantom
conjurer and devotee.
So, we set forth to slay him.
[yells]
Quick! Now's your best chance!
[BISHAMON grunts]
[AIHA yelps]
[KAZUMA]
Aiha!
Oh, no!
Hey! You okay?
Stay very still, Veena.
She'll take your head off.
So I assumed.
[IZANAMI]
Oh, look! This is pretty!
Give him back! Right now!
[IZANAMI] What excellent luck!
It's nearly dinner time.
Come, everyone. We'll
have a feast tonight.
Look at this scrumptious dish.
Plenty for all, ladies!
[BELDAM LADY 10A]
Ooh, yes please!
[BELDAM LADY 10B]
That does look delicious!
[IZANAMI] Come, come.
Eat as much as you'd like.
What are you doing?
Stop! Get away from me!
[BISHAMON screams]
No! Veena!
--Stop!
--[BISHAMON] Get off!
Damn it! Can't get out!
Struggling against it
will only hurt you more.
I've had enough of this!
Lemme go, you old hag!
[EBISU]
Kunimi. Are you all right?
I'll live, but just barely.
If it wasn't for the Yato god...
[sighs]
[KUNIMI]
I hope he'll be okay.
Lady Bishamon just went into
the underworld to save him.
That's something.
Though I don't think even she
is a match for Izanami.
But hold on.
Didn't you just say
there was a way
we could bring him back?
What were you talking about?
[EBISU] It's a method
known as a Soul Call.
[YUKINE]
I don't understand.
[EBISU] You peer into the very
depths of the underworld
and call out someone's
name to fasten them
to the Near Shore. I believe
that's the only way left
to bring him back
from Izanami's realm.
So we just gotta call his name?
You really think
that will do it?
If it doesn't, nothing will.
But it must come from a Near
Shore being with ties to him.
Gods and the deceased
are unable to do it.
Only a human can.
You.
[EBISU] To be honest, I've
never heard of this technique
being used on a god before.
But we've no other choice.
It's worth a try.
[YUKINE]
Good luck. Be careful.
[inhales] Yato!
[IZANAMI]
Go on!
You only have to take one
little bite of the food
of the underworld.
Then you can stay
with me forever!
Won't that be nice?
Go on. Have some!
--[BELDAM LADIES cackling]
--[BISHAMON grunting]
[grunting]
[screams]
[KINUHA]
Hold on. Stay strong!
I'm going to try and
rip her hair off.
[BISHAMON grunting]
Soon. Almost there.
My lady!
[yells]
[BELDAM LADIES scream]
[IZANAMI grunts]
[YATO grunts]
[coughs]
[BISHAMON]
Lady Izanami.
I'm sorry to
interrupt your banquet,
but it's time for us to leave.
The Yato god's coming with me.
[HIYORI]
Bishamonten!
[BISHAMON gasps]
She disappeared. Wait,
could that have been...?
[IZANAMI]
A Soul Call.
It was a Soul Call? So...
I can get outta here if
someone calls my name?
Yes, it would seem so.
[YATO gasps]
[HIYORI]
Yato! Yato!
Milady! Were you
harmed in any way?
Wha... What just happened
to me down there?
Yato! Yato!
Why? He's not coming.
Hey! Look out!
I don't get it!
It worked on Lady
Bishamon but not him?
What's wrong? Why can't
we Soul Call Yato?
That was a Soul Call?
[EBISU]
Well, let's think.
Is it possible that's
not his true name?
[DAIKOKU, KOFUKU,
YUKINE, HIYORI gasp]
So he borrowed one?
Like in the same way
that my lady goes by
Ebisu Kofuku you mean?
That is a possibility.
I do it to obscure my
identity as a god of poverty.
So then, who is Yato?
Damn! Using an alternate name?
He's never talked about that!
That's why it didn't work.
You must call his true name
to bring him back successfully.
Any idea what it could be?
No.
[BISHAMON]
Kazuma?
I can't think of anything.
I'm very sorry.
If we don't do
something swiftly,
Yato will be trapped forever.
[drums]
What is that?
No, it can't be.
[drums]
[BISHAMON]
The heavens' Punishers!
All they have to do
is call my name?
Great! Any minute,
we'll be outta here!
[NORA]
Will we?
Do they know your real name?
Did you ever tell them?
[YATO gasps]
[IZANAMI]
Yato, my dear!
Aren't you getting hungry yet?
[coughs]
[YATO] She's right.
I never told them anything.
I couldn't bring myself to.
[YATO] I knew if I told
them, they'd hate me.
They'd abandon me for sure.
So I stayed silent.
I revealed nothing
about my past.
And that means...
They don't know my real name.
They can't call me
back. I'm trapped.
So it's all over.
If the heavens have chosen to
reject me, then I'm finished.
Who are they? The
heavens' Punishers?
It looks like they're all gods.
The bastards are
hiding their faces.
I guess they don't want anybody
knowing the identity
of Lord Ebisu's killers.
That's disgusting.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Ebisu!
You've already returned
from the underworld, I see.
[GOD 7C]
A Vent!
[GOD 7A] You've opened a
Vent into the underworld?
What exactly are you planning?
[GOD 7B]
Look! It's releasing Phantoms!
[GOD 7C]
We must seal it!
No!
We'll never get Yato out!
[BISHAMON]
Wait, everyone!
I implore you to
give Ebisu a chance
to explain what he has done.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Bishamonten.
Why are you interfering
with our task?
Is it not natural
for me to stand
in support of a
fellow God of Fortune?
I had hoped we might
hear Ebisu's reasons
before resorting
to senseless murder.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI] We are
standing in front of a Vent
that he opened.
We have no need of explanations.
[BISHAMON] Say what you will,
but he has done no wrong!
Bishamon, wait.
I have complete faith in him.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI] The heavens'
decree is not a matter
for debate. If you insist
on protecting him,
you do so at your own risk.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Conjurer Ebisu!
You have violated a taboo and
caused disorder in the heavens.
You are to be cleansed and kept
in the Shrine of Passing!
Once, I would have given in.
But... I am no longer so
accepting of my own death.
How can you be ready
to give up so easily?
Isn't there someone you'll miss?
or maybe something
you wanna do again?
[EBISU] I've finally realized
that there are some things
I'm willing to fight for.
My name will endure
past my death.
For that reason, I have long
taken my lives for granted.
But I'm not ready
to give this one up yet.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Fire!
Defend me, Senki!
[SENKI]
Yes!
[GOD 7A] There's the proof!
He does employ Phantoms!
You've shown yourself
for what you are, conjurer!
Come, Uki! Come, Tekki!
Quickly! Shuki! Sakki! Gaki!
[BISHAMON]
Kinki!
[KURAHA roars]
[grunts]
[PHANTOMS growl]
[yelps]
The Vent!
Kofuku!
Kokki!
Let's give this one
everything we've got!
Yeah!
Bore!
It's no good.
It's still closing!
Please! You need to call
Yatty's real name and quickly!
She can't call it
if we don't know it!
--Whoa, hey!
--[HIYORI] Yato!
[HIYORI] Yato! Please,
you have to come back!
Borderline!
Come on! You'll get
shot, Hiyori!
Yato! Yato!
[HIYORI]
Yato! Yato! Yato!
That obviously isn't his name!
It has to be!
[BOTH gasp]
Remember? That shrine
I made Yato...
He was so happy when he got it.
He said it was what
he always wanted.
I carved his name on it.
How could that name
be the wrong one?
He was so happy, he cried.
I did carve "Yato," right?
[HIYORI gasps]
[inhales]
[HIYORI]
Yaboku!
[YATO gasps]
[gasps]
[GOD 7A]
That light! What's happening?
[gasps]
[YATO grunts]
You... called me.
I did.
[HIYORI, YATO, YUKINE sigh]
It really worked! You're here.
I'm here. Thanks to you.
[IZANAMI] Alone again.
Will no one ever stay with me?
[GOD 7B]
He summoned something
from the underworld!
[GOD 7D]
Dispatch it quickly!
Are you okay?
[YATO]
I think so.
You came all this way
to look for me?
[grunts]
Ebisu! You're in bad shape.
You and the others fall back.
You don't stand a chance
against the Punishers.
I can still fight.
Get moving. I'll hold them off.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
You shall not escape. Come, Oki!
[KIUN roars]
That's Kiun,
Takemikazuchi's Regalia.
Young Master!
Kiun is also known
as the Thunder Blade,
and for good reason.
Your Phantoms won't be
able to stand before him.
[PHANTOMS groan]
[ALL screaming]
[YATO grunts]
What's with them?
They're pissed.
I'm sorry for this.
Are you okay?
You're still alive!
How did you do that?
Ebisu, just go!
[KURAHA roars]
Thanks, my friend.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Running will do no good.
[yells]
[BISHAMON]
Where'd everyone go?
[KAZUMA]
Into the forest.
[BISHAMON]
All right. Kazuma.
Push Kinuha's Borderlines
to maximum power.
We're going to take out Kiun.
[KIUN growls]
What? We can't take him out!
[KAZUMA]
Are you certain?
Kazuma?
Yes, I am.
Demonstrate your dominance,
my Blessed Vessel.
Yes.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
You may be a Blessed Vessel,
but I am not threatened
by a mere earring.
[KIUN roars]
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI gasps]
[KIUN growling]
We really hit him!
[KAZUMA]
Not enough.
I need to reach
further than that.
[KAZUMA] I must exceed his
Borderlines and strike deeper.
I must believe that I am
the dominant Regalia here.
[KAZUMA, BISHAMON]
And seize control!
[KIUN roars]
[GODS groaning]
[EBISU sighs]
A frightening display.
That is what true
power looks like.
Bishamonten and
her Blessed Vessel.
[YATO panting]
Is it bad?
[YUKINE]
Yato!
Yeah, Yukine?
[YUKINE]
Who the hell is Yaboku?
And since when is "Yato"
not your real name, huh?
How could you have lied
to us this whole time?
It's complicated.
Can we do this later?
I have to know.
Why'd you go into the underworld
without saying a
single word to us?
You just disappeared one day
and went and got yourself
beaten to death!
With all we've been though,
you still don't trust me.
You're an idiot, you know that?
And a terrible master.
Okay, that's enough.
Listen to me, I...
[YATO gasps] No. Let go of me!
You'll get blighted, too!
--[YUKINE] Yato.
--Stop--
[YUKINE]
I know I haven't always been
the best Regalia, but,
but I made an oath.
In case you've forgotten,
I swore I would
risk my name to protect you!
I haven't forgotten.
You're his Blessed Vessel.
[rumbling]
You guys, what's happening?
[ALL screaming]
Is that what I think?
A Pacification Ring!
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
There you are.
The next one won't miss, Ebisu.
[GODS] How pure is the
brightness of thy soul.
How pure the brightness of
thy heart. How pure it is.
In the name of Takagi-no-kami,
we wield the
heavenly wax-tree bow.
Incredible.
I can't believe they're actually
using a Pacification Ring!
I've never heard of that before.
It's something used to quell
the enemies of the heavens.
A very ancient art.
One hit from that thing
and we're all dead.
I can't believe how far
they're willing to take this.
This is insane!
There's no reason for them to
drag the mortal world into it.
[YATO]
Sekki!
What are you doing?
[YATO] You're the one they're
going to all this trouble for.
The thing is, you made a wish
and I haven't granted it yet.
Another meal at the
Olive Tavern, remember?
[gasps]
You're kidding!
But you're not in
any condition to be--
[YATO] I refuse to let
them have their way!
I know that I can trust
you. Now, let's go!
[GODS] Should thou be of
pure heart, god Ebisu.
Should thou be pure of soul,
the arrow shall miss.
Should thou be dark of heart,
the arrow shall
tear thee asunder.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Farewell, Ebisu.
Look out! It's coming!
[yelling]
Rend!
[GODS screaming]
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
He cut through it? Impossible!
[YATO grunting]
[KOFUKU yelps]
[HIYORI yelps]
[grunts, coughs] That was
incredible! Yato god!
He truly is fearless.
And so is his Blessed Vessel.
Veena, look!
No! Run, Ebisu!
[cackles]
[YATO] Today, we'll
teach you how to make
fluffy-fluff accessories.
[YUKINE]
First, get some cotton fabric.
[HIYORI] Then you just
take it and rip it up.
[YATO]
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"The God of Fortune's Message."
[YUKINE]
Here. You take it, Yato.
[YATO]
You're not gonna wear it?
But it's so stylish! Come on!