[MAYU gasps]
[KOFUKU crying]
[KOFUKU]
Welcome home!
You made it! Oh, I'm so happy!
I thought you were
goners for sure!
And the rest?
Lady Bishamon and the others?
They're safe, too.
They got some things
out in the open.
Hopefully, that means
she'll stop hounding me.
None of this has been easy.
But, personally,
I couldn't be happier.
No more crazy
war god on my tail!
And even better than that...
I've finally got myself
a Blessed Vessel.
[TENJIN, REGALIA]
Wha?
[KOFUKU]
Really?
--[MAYU] Seriously?
--[DAIKOKU] No way!
[TENJIN]
For that wretch?
--[YATO laughs]
--[YUKINE laughs nervously]
[MAYU] No one has
ever deserved it less!
That kid's too
good for you, Yato.
A Blessed Vessel?
It's something pretty rare.
Yukki risked his name
to protect his master.
Just like what Kazu
did for Bisha.
They're very special Regalia.
So, you've finally
found the one for you.
That must make you happy.
Kinda.
[DAIKOKU]
All right!
We're celebratin' tonight!
Let's go prep for a party!
[KOFUKU]
Woo-hoo!
That reminds me...
Uh-oh!
Oh, no! My advancement
exam is today!
I'm sorry! I really have to go!
[TENJIN] If you'd wait
a moment please, Hiyori.
Yes, what is it?
Well, Yato?
About our agreement.
I trust you remember.
[YATO]
Please, Tenjin.
Just take us up there.
This is for Hiyori.
[TENJIN] I'll agree to help
you on two conditions.
First, no one is to know
I was involved in any way.
As for the second...
I assume you know.
[TENJIN]
Now that you've returned safely,
you are to sever your ties
with her once and for all.
No...
You actually agreed to that?
[TENJIN] It's become
painfully obvious that
Yato's involved you too
much with the Far Shore.
That entanglement has
repeatedly placed you
in unnecessary danger.
Lord Tenjin, I don't think--
[TENJIN]
You are not yet one of the dead.
You must send her back where
she belongs now, Yato.
It is the right thing to do.
You know it is.
Sekki.
You're going to cut our ties?
Are you sure, Yato?
I'll forget you, though.
It'll be like we never even met.
And you're okay with that?
Well, I'm not.
Don't do it. You can't!
It's not fair!
Please! Yato!
I'm not ready to lose you yet!
[YAMA]
I gotta say.
These uniforms are a whole lot
cuter than our old ones were.
Yeah!
I wasn't sure I liked
them that much at first,
but I think they're
growing on me.
You know, Hiyori,
for a little while there
it looked like you weren't
even gonna graduate.
You only barely woke up
in time to take the exam.
[laughs nervously]
What about you?
You were wide awake,
and you still almost failed.
Yeah, I don't wanna
talk about it, thanks.
Heh.
So, what club
are you gonna join?
[YAMA]
I still haven't decided.
[AMI] Tennis or basketball...
Or a Culture Club, maybe.
What do you think?
Hm. I'm not really sure.
[YATO]
What'll she join?
The Yato Club, of course!
[YAMA]
What's up, Hiyori?
Join now and guess what?
You can get your very
own fluffy-fluff scarf!
[HIYORI grumbles]
Hey, where's the fire?
Maybe she's joining
the Track Club.
Yato Club! Yato Club!
Yato Club, Yo!
[AMI, YAMA scream]
[AMI]
There it is!
Her first Insta-Snooze
in this grade!
Yo! Where you goin'?
The Yato Club is
looking for you!
Will you please
stop following me?
Come on, you idiot!
What are we doing?
[YATO]
Yato Club! Yato Club! Yato Club!
[HIYORI groans]
Leave me alone!
[YUKINE]
Listen to her!
If I had to guess, I'd say...
...they haven't
severed their ties.
[sighs] Yato's hopeless.
Honestly, Mayu, I don't
know why I even bother.
What does he intend to do now?
[TSUYU]
My lord.
Huh?
It's time.
We must be on our way soon.
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Lady Bishamon.
God of war though you may be,
your recent actions
are unacceptable.
[GOD 7A]
This isn't the Month of Gods!
To have a Colloquy now?
It's unheard of!
[GOD 7B] Your corruption
and its aftermath
have caused a tumult.
You have shaken
the very heavens.
How do you explain
your behavior?
The Yato god's attack
was unexpected.
I admit, I responded poorly.
[GOD 7C]
Do you mean the snake god?
Yato-no-kami?
Certainly not!
I've no part in this.
A charlatan must
be using my name!
Indeed, you're right.
It was not you I meant.
I speak of a nameless
god without a shrine.
[GOD 7C]
Oh, yes.
There are some like that.
Wretches who seek to
benefit from others' status.
[GOD 7D]
True. As a matter of fact,
I believe a god of poverty
is using Lord Ebisu's name.
[GOD 7B]
What I would like to know
is how a shrine-less one
was able to ascend here
in the first place.
[coughs]
Never mind this nameless god.
He's of no concern.
The Masked Ones are, however.
Masked Ones...
Phantoms employed
using Scourges.
Never before has one appeared
here in Takamagahara.
What of this Kugaha
who brought them?
Why did you decide
to release him?
[GOD 7A]
Indeed.
From him, we could have
learned about the conjurer
who created the Masked Ones.
Perhaps I acted hastily.
However, you may be
interested to know
that I have since
learned he was not bound
by the name "Kuga." I presume
he was the conjurer's Nora.
[GODS gasping, murmuring]
A Nora, you say?
You believe someone here
granted him a name.
Is that your accusation?
Nothing like that!
It isn't my intention to
accuse anyone of anything.
What troubles me is
this conjurer's ingenuity
and ability to deceive the gods!
This incident has unsettled
both Heaven and Earth.
There will be consequences.
Phantom numbers will increase.
You are to carefully observe
every Phantom's behavior.
I expect timely reports
regarding any
Masked Ones you find.
I will issue a search
notice for this Kugaha.
The Colloquy is adjourned.
[REGALIA 7A whispering]
So, she really was corrupted?
[REGALIA 7B whispering]
And he's still her exemplar?
Even after failing her twice?
[BISHAMON]
I'm finished. Finally.
You must be exhausted.
[BISHAMON sighs]
I admit, it is fatiguing.
I know I am at fault
for what happened.
But as a god, I cannot afford
to bow down to others.
I understand their
displeasure, though.
There's no trace of Kugaha.
No one knows where he is.
If he truly is a Nora,
as we suspect,
he may already have
returned to another master.
Most likely the one
who created the masks.
Naming and employing Phantoms...
Who would do such a thing?
It's essentially like
asking to be corrupted.
That's inconceivable.
[BISHAMON]
Truly.
How could such a god
continue to exist?
Unless... the one
responsible is already
something that shouldn't exist.
[OKUNINUSHI]
Bishamon!
--[BISHAMON] Hm?
--Good to see ya!
How's it goin'?
[BISHAMON]
Okuninushi! Everyone!
[REGALIA 7C]
Oh! All Seven Gods of Fortune!
Those grouchy bastards.
Glad that's over.
Thought those geezers would
never leave you alone!
My ears need a break after that.
Yours, too, Inaba?
[INABA squeaks]
[BISHAMON]
Everyone can hear you.
Let 'em listen!
Anyway, forget all that.
Since we've got the
whole gang together again,
I'm throwin' a party at my
shrine in Hawaii! Wanna come?
Where's Ebisu?
He was just here a second ago.
Anybody know where he went?
Ah, go figure.
I don't know what that guy's
up to half the time, anyway.
Well, drop by if you can.
You know where we'll be.
It's gonna be awesome! Aloha!
A party. Will you go?
No. I'll pass.
[EBISU]
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Ebisu, of the
Seven Gods of Fortune.
I'm here today because I have
heard some stories about you.
I have a proposition to make.
Iwami.
Sir.
[EBISU] I would like to
purchase your Blessed Vessel.
[IWAMI]
Is it insufficient?
I can bring you another
briefcase, master.
[UTAMI, KUNIMI, TATSUMI gasp]
Boss!
Wake up, Yato god.
I want Yukine. I am
willing to pay any price.
Uh... Any price at all?
You're not really gonna sell me!
Even you wouldn't do that!
Yukine.
If you do join me, I'll pay
you one million a month.
Ow.
I know that sting!
You're feeling
greedy, aren't ya?
Don't you try to
hide it from me!
Maybe it was just
a static shock.
You are behaving
distastefully, Sir Yukine.
You should not be so
easily swayed by money.
It's unbecoming of an exemplar.
An exemplar? Who? Wait, me?
That's correct.
You are Lord Yato's unique,
irreplaceable Regalia.
And that makes you
the same as an exemplar.
An exemplar leads the way.
He serves his god
as a guide of virtue.
In short, he is a half-god.
Lose your way, and your
master will surely perish.
You must be steadfast.
Indeed. Your position is vital.
It is you who protects
Lord Yato's name.
Perhaps you could
see about acquiring
the services of a
different exemplar.
Or perhaps we
could share Yukine.
I would welcome his
talent, even as a Nora.
Uh...
It's rather sad.
A god residing
in another's abode.
And surely a Blessed Vessel
deserves better than that.
Have you no shrine
of your own, Yato god?
[phone vibrating]
[sighs]
[HIYORI groans]
[HIYORI]
Enough!
I'm not joining the Yato Club!
Um, where did all
of that come from?
Oh, you mean the money?
[HIYORI gasps]
Don't tell me...?
What do you take me for?
That stone-faced creep, Ebisu,
randomly showed up here.
He wanted to buy Yukine from me.
Told me to take the money
and build a shrine.
Real nice guy.
[HIYORI]
How could you do that to him?
I didn't sell Yukine!
Have some faith in me, will ya?
I don't need somebody else's
help to build my shrine.
But, you know, it's possible
Yukine will decide he'd
rather go with Ebisu.
It's a confusing time.
Kid's all mixed up inside.
[YUKINE] So, I learned something
from Lord Ebisu today.
[gasps] Yeah? What was it?
[YUKINE] Apparently...
I'm Yato's exemplar.
Crazy, huh?
[DAIKOKU]
Not that crazy. I'm one, too.
[YUKINE, HIYORI]
What? You are?
[DAIKOKU]
Uh-huh.
[YUKINE] But I thought
exemplars were like, you know,
leaders and stuff.
Really respectable,
upstanding Regalia...
[DAIKOKU]
Unlike me?
It's true that an exemplar
sets the standard
for righteousness when
there are lots of Regalia,
but I'm Kofuku's only one.
Just like you're
Yato's only Regalia.
Right. His only one.
[DAIKOKU] And remember,
Kofuku's a god of poverty
who spreads disaster.
She isn't helpless.
She doesn't need much
protecting, so she says.
My lady is always telling me I
shouldn't risk my name for her.
All I need to do is raise
her when she reincarnates.
That's my duty as her exemplar.
It's how I protect her.
Now, Lord Ebisu relies
on his exemplar, Iwami,
to see that his
wishes are passed on.
His reincarnations
and Regalia changes
tend to be pretty intense.
And then there's Kazuma.
You know how devoted
he is to Lady Bishamon.
Exemplars all have their own way
of protecting their masters.
And none of them are wrong.
Question is, how do you
want to protect Yato?
So, um.
What are you gonna
do with the money?
I'm gonna give it all back!
What else would I do?
[phone rings]
Hello and thank you for calling!
Fast, affordable, and reliable.
Delivery God Yato
at your service!
So, how can I help you?
[BOY 7A]
S-Sorry, I, um...
Uh... Hey, um.
I'm pretty sure
this is a job offer,
but it sounds kinda dirty,
if you know what I mean.
You can't afford to
be picky about work!
--You slacker!
--[YATO yelping]
--[yelping]
--Oh please, God! Don't hurt us!
Please, God. Please,
God. Please, God.
What the--?
[YATO]
The client's grandmother
was the victim of a
bank transfer scam.
[YUKINE] Wouldn't she be better
off just going to the police?
[YATO] She doesn't wanna make
a big deal of it, apparently.
Hey. Five yen isn't
a lot of money.
You ever think about raising
your rate a little bit?
What, and stop getting
clients altogether?
Forget that!
I'm trying to get
my name out there.
I want people who believe
in me. Not money.
[sighs] A little money
wouldn't hurt, though.
You, too? Typical!
My Regalia are always
quitting because of money.
I don't get it.
Humans seem to be incurably
fixated on the stuff.
Why should you be any different?
Go join Ebisu for all I care!
[YUKINE]
Oh! Now I see!
With Regalia always leaving,
you don't have much choice.
You have to turn to Nora.
[gasps]
Makes perfect sense.
That's why you haven't
gotten rid of her.
You need her as your fallback.
That's kinda sad, actually.
[tires sqeak]
Here we go.
That's the post office box the
old woman sent the money to.
He's our man.
Sekki.
Sekki!
Man, old people
are such suckers!
Uh. I'm not seeing
a Phantom, here.
[YATO]
Yep! There it is.
The size of a flea!
We'll cut only the Phantom.
[YATO grunting]
[YUKINE]
No good.
It's too small for me to cut.
In that case...
[YATO yelps]
Wait!
[COIN PURSE PHANTOM 7A]
Geezer. More. More.
[gasps]
[YUKINE]
What was that?
[YATO] I think that Phantom's
got a thing for money.
Money, huh?
[YATO panting]
[YUKINE] Yato! You've
gotta revert me! Hurry!
[YATO]
Huh?
[YUKINE]
Just do it!
And you keep
chasing the Phantom.
[YUKINE panting]
Back already?
Is Yatty with you?
[rustling]
Hey, what are you doing up here?
[YUKINE]
Acting like an exemplar should.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
I can't let myself
become fixated on money.
I need to remember
I've got a job to do.
I can't put my desires first.
Wait, I'm coming, too!
[THIEF 7A, MEN laughing]
[THIEF 7A]
So easy!
[COIN PURSE PHANTOM 7A]
Want more.
Not enough.
Want a lot more.
[THIEF 7A]
Look! Money!
It's raining money!
What the hell are you
doing with my money?
[HIYORI]
He's got a plan, right?
Money! My sweet money!
[groaning]
I don't know much about
it yet, but I'd guess
an exemplar isn't supposed
to give into greed.
[DAIKOKU]
How do you want to protect Yato?
Who will be your exemplar?
If the choice is
between me, and her...
...then it should be me.
Wow, kid, you've really changed.
[THIEF 7A]
Woo-hoo!
Money-money-money! Gimme more!
[COIN PURSE PHANTOM 7A]
More! More! More!
More!
[COIN PURSE PHANTOM 7A]
That's a big one!
All right! The Phantom
took the bait. Let's go!
[gasps]
Dude! You're still
stuffing your pockets?
"Who needs money?"
You act all high and mighty,
but you were gonna sell me!
C'mon, admit it, you were!
I'd never sell you, I swear!
I do want money, though!
So the truth comes out, huh?
[YATO]
I need money for a shrine!
[YUKINE] Why are you so
obsessed with having a shrine?
As your exemplar, I feel
I should make a suggestion.
Throw the money away, Yato.
[YATO]
Sekki! Let's go!
[YUKINE]
Yeah!
[COIN PURSE PHANTOM 7A]
Want more!
[YATO]
Ha!
[COIN PURSE PHANTOM 7A]
More money! Want more money!
[YATO] This is the land
of the Rising Sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me. I am the god, Yato.
I now lay thee waste
with the Sekki,
and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
[COIN PURSE PHANTOM 7A]
More money!
[YATO grunts]
[HIYORI'S MOM]
A bank transfer scam?
How awful! Be careful, Hiyori.
You never know who you
can trust these days.
Yeah.
[HIYORI'S MOM]
Money is nice, but as they say,
it can't buy happiness.
Ah.
I need to go take a look
in my brother's room.
[KOFUKU]
Well done!
I hear you turned
down Ebi's offer.
I'm proud of you.
This kid's really startin'
to grow up on us.
Way to go, Yukine!
So... where's Yato?
[sighs]
He really wanted a shrine.
He's pretty bummed out about it.
This is some hardcore pouting.
You know he's really upset
when he refuses to eat.
[HIYORI] Yato, is a shrine
really that important?
[YATO]
Yeah, it is.
If you don't have one,
it's like no one cares
about you or anything you do.
[HIYORI]
All right, then.
Here. This is for you.
Whoa.
A mini shrine?
You made it, Yori?
That's right!
I used my brother's materials.
I actually had a lot
of fun doing it.
I was up working all night.
[KOFUKU]
Wow!
Hey, this is awesome!
You finally got
yourself a shrine.
I hope it'll cheer you up.
He-He's crying?
[gasps]
[YUKINE] Why are you so
obsessed with having a shrine?
It's my dream, okay?
I've always wanted one.
Ever since I was little.
But no one would ever
build one for me.
[KOFUKU] Humans may not think
much about it, but being given
a shrine is a very
big honor for us.
Because there're people
who believe in us.
People who appreciate us.
For a god, not much
matters more than that.
Hey, man, watch the snot!
Tissues! We need
tissues! Aw, geez!
You're gonna get snot
all over your new shrine!
So, the Yato god
can't be persuaded
to let go of his
Blessed Vessel. Hmph.
[OKUNINUSHI] Ebisu!
Join me for a drink tonight!
[EBISU]
Very well.
What time would you like
to meet for this drink?
[OKUNINUSHI]
You know, whenever.
[EBISU] On the next Noragami
Aragoto: "God of Calamity."
And how big is this drink?
If there are two
of us, it must be--
[OKUNINUSHI] I don't think
you get the concept.