[TEACHER 10A]
I'm sure you already studied
basic factorization
in junior high.
Good news: the method
remains the same.
Think of the
process as splitting
an expression into smaller,
more manageable expressions.
[STUDENT 10A]
No way. Seriously?
[STUDENTS giggle]
[ABE] Things went pretty
well at Capypa Land,
so I invited her to a
Hundred Archfiends concert.
Wait, Hiyori!
[HIYORI panting]
[HIYORI cries]
[sighs]
[YUKINE]
Hiyori! It's been awhile!
Oh, you've switched uniforms.
Is it that time of year already?
[HIYORI]
Uh...
[YUKINE] It's easy to
lose track of that stuff
in Takamagahara.
Anyway, I've been
really busy studying
invocations with Kazuma.
So I haven't exactly had time
to finish the homework
you assigned me.
I'm so sorry!
You understand, right?
Maybe I could get an extension?
I, uh...
Wait, that says Yuki... Yukine.
Yep. That is my name.
[HIYORI]
Yukine!
[YUKINE]
Whoa, hey!
[HIYORI]
This smell, this nice smell.
I remember everything!
Yukine, Yato,
the promise I made!
I can't believe I
almost forgot all of it!
[YUKINE]
Hey! What's up with you?
[YUKINE] Geez! You're an idiot!
What were you thinking?
Don't ever do
that again, Hiyori!
'Kay. Sorry.
[HIYORI] So, anyway. What's
Yato been up to these days?
How should I know?
It's been more than a month now
since I heard from the guy.
I wouldn't waste my time
worrying. What a big jerk.
[HIYORI]
Gone a whole month?
My lady hasn't
come back yet either.
Hi, Daikoku.
Oh, hey, Hiyori.
Long time no see, huh?
She still isn't back?
Hasn't it been awhile?
Yeah.
I haven't heard from her
since I was sent home
from the latest Colloquy.
It's weird, too.
They usually can't stand
the sight of her there.
I don't like this.
I know. Kazuma feels
the same way.
He says it's strange there've
been all these meetings.
[HIYORI] There are so many
entries in my date book
about them. And then they
just suddenly stopped.
I hope everything--
What're you doing?
[HIYORI] I'm gonna go
out and look for Yato.
[YUKINE]
Wait, you're gonna do what?
Hold on! Hiyori!
[HIYORI]
I almost forgot him once before.
But I was so stupid
and cocky this time.
Yato!
[HIYORI] Idiot! I was so
sure I would never forget.
Like I was different
or special somehow.
Because our ties
hadn't been cut.
But I'm not an exception at all!
[KOFUKU] It's totally different
for unknown gods like Yatty.
Once they've been forgotten,
they vanish from existence.
Yato!
[HIYORI]
I don't even know where to look.
Because, the truth is,
I don't know Yato at all.
Stay with me! Stay!
[YATO] Damn it! What are
these creepy things?
They must be Izanami's Beldams.
They're under her control.
Don't let them
catch you, understand?
You'll be trapped here forever.
[EBISU]
Yuki! Hold them off.
[YUKI]
Sir.
That was incredible.
The brush really does work.
It allowed me to summon
a Phantom using only a name.
That's enough "ooh-ing"
and "ah-ing"!
We need to get away from them!
How do we even get outta here?
It's almost
labyrinthine, isn't it?
I think it's more than that.
It's like the whole
place is expanding.
[IZANAMI]
Why are you running away?
We'll be good friends
if you'll stay with me.
[YATO] Hey! Earlier, when
we first tried to leave,
you called her "Mother."
If you're her son,
can't you do something?
I wanted to discover more
about my own origins,
so I consulted
the old literature.
One story says that
she abandoned me.
If that's true, then she
clearly didn't want me.
So I don't know
how our relationship
will make any difference.
It's got me!
[YATO grunts]
They can't be cut!
Just let go, damn it!
[UTAMI, TATSUMI yell]
[TATSUMI]
Young Mast--!
[BELDAM LADIES cackling]
Tatsumi! Utami!
[BELDAM LADY 10A]
Ooh, I want it!
[BELDAM LADY 10B]
No, he's mine!
[BELDAM LADY 10C]
I saw him first!
[YATO]
Come on!
[EBISU panting]
Hiiro. How could you?
He got away, didn't he?
You should be thankful.
[NORA] Now we can
fulfill Father's request.
You're the conjurer
we were sent to rescue.
[YATO] I have to get
Ebisu out at all costs.
Why do you want him
so badly, old man?
What's your game?
[EBISU]
Yato god.
I should be all right
now. Let's go.
All the previous
Ebisus died for this.
I must leave here with
the Locution Brush.
Why are you so obsessed with it?
Your other
incarnations are dead.
Their work can die with them.
This is what I am meant to do!
It's my purpose.
Is that something
you can understand?
[EBISU] The world is filled
with senseless violence
and unnecessary pain. That's
why we gods are so important.
But with this Locution Brush,
I'll be able to restrain
Phantoms and prevent
at least some of the
misfortune they cause.
I can use it to make
the world a better,
less painful place to live.
Does that answer your question?
[EBISU grunts]
[panting]
[YATO]
All this, for humanity's sake?
I didn't think guys like
that actually existed.
[IZANAMI]
Where are you?
Where did my friends go?
[YATO]
This whole time I assumed he was
doing it for power.
[YATO] Such a fierce will.
I'll never have that.
[NORA]
You're a god of calamity.
Don't you see?
This is the sort of work
you should be doing.
[MOTHER 8A]
Thank you...
[NORA] People appreciate this
type of job a lot more.
[NORA]
Well done. Very well done, Yato.
[EBISU grunts]
[BELDAM LADIES, IZANAMI]
Found you!
[YATO] I've always done
everything I was told to do.
It just seemed easier that way.
But that's gonna change.
I wanna be someone
people respect.
Someone who she can be
proud to have in her life!
[BELDAM LADIES screaming]
Kunimi! Go! Take Ebisu
and get outta here!
What? Wait. You
can't kill Izanami.
Don't have to kill her.
I just have to hold her off.
That much I can do.
[HIYORI]
Yato-no-Kami.
His name is similar,
but he can't be our Yato.
He has a shrine and
even appears in stories.
[gasps]
[HIYORI] It looks like
Ebisu has multiple names.
Huh.
[HIYORI] And Bishamonten
also goes by Vaisravana?
Huh. Strange.
I wonder if Yato has
another name, too.
There are so many gods
described in these books,
but I can't find anything
that even mentions him.
There's nothing online, either.
All I can see are his
social network pages.
I know! I'll ask Mayu.
[MAYU]
The heavens are in disorder?
Yes. I just returned
from Lord Ebisu's estate.
They have the whole
area cordoned off,
and I was even threatened
by armed Sentinels.
[REGALIA gasp]
Wait, what's a sentinel?
They're the Regalia
that serve the heavens.
But Sentinels aren't
usually armed.
Something really big
must be going on.
We were there recently.
So I know Lord Ebisu
has been corrupted.
It's likely he'll perish again.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] The heavens
have always tolerated
his excessive corruptions
and reincarnations.
But not this time. For some
reason, this is different.
Yeah, no doubt.
[KAZUMA] Hm. I was hoping
to ask for your help, Tsuyu.
You can find out
what's happening
in Takamagahara, and with
more certainty than I can.
Will you please
consider helping us?
No, Sir Kazuma.
I cannot afford to jeopardize
my lord's standing.
We should wait to receive
word before doing anything.
Or do you mean to
antagonize the heavens?
They have the Gods of Fortune.
They're likely being questioned.
Perhaps even being tortured.
I understand.
I know how it is to fear
for one's master. Very well.
What? What's this?
[MAYU] Tsuyu is speaking
with the trees.
She isn't a Regalia, you know.
She's the spirit of a plum tree.
[YUKINE gasps]
[MAYU] It is said that, long
ago, she traveled all the way
to Dazaifu to be
with Lord Tenjin.
She's been his companion since.
For more than 1,000 years.
Her affection for him is deep,
and it will not ever wither.
[TSUYU]
Conjurer. Masks. Phantoms.
Echoes of discord
among the gods.
The heavens are searching for
Lord Ebisu and his exemplar.
Really?
[gasps]
[TSUYU] There is a peach tree
located near the Verge.
It saw Lord Ebisu head
into the underworld.
The underworld?
What could possibly
send him there?
[TSUYU]
He had pursuers.
[DAIKOKU, KAZUMA gasp]
[TSUYU] A young male god
with a lean frame
and a short girl in
white wearing a crown.
That's--
[HIYORI]
Nora. It must be, right?
That sounds like Yato and Nora.
[OKUNINUSHI]
Oshi!
Just how long you
gonna keep us locked up
in this damn place?
[OSHI] We have just discovered
that Lord Ebisu is,
indeed, the conjurer. An edict
has been issued for his death.
Punishment for
disrupting the heavens.
What?
[FUKUROKUJU grunts]
[JUROJIN, HOTEI gasp]
How are you so sure it's him?
[OSHI] We conducted a
search of his residence
and found a large
number of masks there.
He also had many Phantoms
in his care, evidently.
Furthermore, we discovered
that most of his Regalia
are actually Noras. Disgraceful.
But what of Ebisu?
[OSHI] Lord Ebisu
appears to have ventured
into the underworld.
Likely to procure more
Phantoms, we suspect.
That sounds like
a bunch of crap.
I don't believe it.
[OSHI]
It is fact, I assure you.
Lord Ebisu is guilty.
His Regalia confessed everything
after being interrogated.
Interrogated? What did you do?
That's none of your concern.
The heavens now intend
to call upon the gods.
Lord Ebisu's behavior
must be punished.
By death?
Why go straight to
capital punishment?
It won't be easy
to help him now.
Not with the edict in place.
It's over. He'll die.
[OKUNINUSHI]
I'm not givin' in that easily.
Huh?
I won't argue with you
about your damn edict.
But if anybody is gonna
kill him, it's gonna be me.
Okuninushi?
[OSHI]
I'm afraid that won't do.
You will remain here until
the situation is resolved.
This way we can
assure your innocence.
You must see that cooperation
is in your best interest.
[OKUNINUSHI]
Outta my way.
Go on. You heard me, now, move.
I'm bein' nice and
respectful to you
at the moment. But remember,
I have gone to war
with the heavens before.
They called me the Bear!
The Spider! Everyone feared me!
Do something!
You have to stop him!
[laughs nervously]
[OKUNINUSHI] Is this what
you want? Another fight?
A god without a
Regalia is helpless.
[KAZUMA]
Restraint!
[grunts]
Forgive my tardiness.
Are you well, my lady?
Kazuma! I'm glad to see you!
[KAZUMA] I wouldn't
expect reinforcements.
They seem a bit
under the weather.
A god without a Regalia
is helpless, you say?
That's a dangerous
thing to assert.
Really, High Sentinel Oshi.
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] I may be willing
to forget you said it.
Assuming that you withdraw now.
I believe she gets
the point, Kazuma.
Benzaiten. Can you handle
things here without me?
Go!
While Fukurokuju sacrifices
himself to Okuninushi!
We may become the
Six Gods of Fortune.
Wait! I didn't agree to this!
[yelps]
We need to get to
Ebisu quickly. Choki!
[KURAHA roars]
[HIYORI]
Let's see.
The Underworld Entrance
is that way.
It's 20 minutes on foot.
You up for a walk?
The entrance to the
underworld is a tourist spot.
Pretty crazy, huh?
[HIYORI] You're being really
quiet. You still upset?
Yato passed through
here, I'm sure.
The others said there was
no guarantee it was him,
but I think it must have been.
Besides, it's our only lead.
Something's going on with him,
and I wanna know what.
I want to hear it from him.
[sighs]
Like I said before,
I really don't think
you should come with me.
You can be majorly stubborn
sometimes, you know that?
[HIYORI sighs]
[YUKINE] What are you
waiting for? Let's go.
[gasps] You're letting me come?
[YUKINE] Yes. But don't do
anything dangerous, you got it?
You're really important to Yato.
To both of us, honestly.
No matter what.
I swear I'm gonna keep you safe.
[cackles]
[YATO grunts]
[IZANAMI]
Would you like some tea?
Something to eat?
Come. We'll have a nice chat.
We need to split apart
and purge the Beldams.
But what about Izanami?
[YATO]
I don't need to kill her.
Just be sure you
maintain your blade!
[NORA]
All right. I will.
[BELDAM LADIES screaming]
We need to buy him enough time
to get outta here
with that brush!
[KUNIMI] Young Master,
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
I'm fine, I think. But you
must be in pain, too, though.
I'm little more than
an encumbrance now.
I owe the Yato god
a great debt for this.
You'll help me remember
that, won't you?
[EBISU] Wha...? What's this
smell? Salty, like blood.
[KUNIMI]
No. Not blood. It's the sea!
We're nearly outside.
Iwami will be waiting for us.
[EBISU panting]
[gasps]
[BELDAM LADY 10A]
Oh, dear.
It seems all the
exits are sealed.
[BELDAM LADY 10B]
Come, let's return
to Lady Izanami now.
I can't fight so many.
This is the end.
[REGALIA 10A]
The new young master certainly
loves playing by the water.
[REGALIA 10B] What little
boy doesn't love fishing?
I only hope he'll live
long enough that we won't
need to call him the
young master anymore.
[EBISU]
Hm?
[REGALIA 10C]
True.
He reincarnates so frequently
compared to other gods.
I wonder why.
[EBISU]
What's reincarnate?
[REGALIA 10A]
To go away and then come back.
[EBISU]
I don't understand.
It's what happens
when a god dies.
[REGALIA 10A]
It's okay, don't worry.
You are a very
famous god, Lord Ebisu.
[REGALIA 10B] A god like
you will always be reborn
after he dies.
[REGALIA 10C] See? There's
no reason to be scared.
Young Master.
Borderline!
It won't open.
I don't get it.
This should be
the entrance. Damn it!
--Borderline! Borderline!
--[HIYORI] Yato...
[IZANAMI chuckles]
It's over. I've caught you.
There's no escaping,
precious one.
You fool.
Didn't I warn you not
to let her catch you?
[IZANAMI]
Now, then. Have a little taste.
[YATO]
This is it. I'm dead.
[EBISU]
Lady Izanami!
[YATO gasps]
[EBISU]
Please, release him. Take me.
I'll remain here
with you instead.
[gasps] You will?
That's wonderful!
[YATO grunts]
Hey, what are you doing? Ebisu!
[EBISU] Yato god.
Take the Locution Brush.
I know that I can trust you.
Just make sure Iwami
gets this, all right?
Huh?
[EBISU] Kunimi is in
dire straits as well.
I'd appreciate it if
you'd take him with you.
Wait, what about you?
[EBISU]
I imagine I'll die before long.
[YATO gasps]
[EBISU]
It's okay.
I'll simply be born again,
as I always am.
So, please.
I don't accept that.
All of this will be completely
pointless if you die!
I wanna help you.
Do you understand?
And not because
someone told me to!
Why do you wanna die so badly?
I don't actively want to die,
but since I just reincarnate,
what does it matter if I do?
What about you as an individual?
Is dying here really
what you want?
Is it really what
this you wants?
[EBISU]
This me? What do you mean?
[YATO]
Isn't there anyone you'll miss?
Someone you wanna see again?
Something you wanna do again?
[EBISU]
Something I want to do again.
I'm not sure.
I suppose I'd like
to eat another meal
at the Olive Tavern.
[YATO]
That'll do.
You have made a wish,
and it has been heard
loud and clear. You can
pay me five yen later.
[growls]
Curse you!
[EBISU] We can't escape
her. We're trapped.
The exits have all been sealed.
[YATO] Don't you wanna
master controlling Phantoms?
How can you be ready
to give up so easily?
[grunting]
[YATO]
If there's no exit, make one.
Drill yourself a
hole outta here!
That's completely crazy.
Don't blame me for
whatever comes next.
Uki! Tekki! Shuki!
Sakki! Gaki! Senki!
Go open a Vent, now!
[PHANTOMS]
As you wish!
[gasps]
[EBISU grunting]
Damn, he actually
opened a Vent. Ha!
[coughs] I'm burning up.
I can't breathe.
[YATO]
Ebisu!
[EBISU]
Yato god?
[yelps]
[gasps]
[YUKINE]
Meow! Meow!
[HIYORI]
Um, what are you doing, Yukine?
[YUKINE]
Practicing cat language.
I'm gonna ask Yato if I can
have a pet cat someday.
[HIYORI] On the next
Noragami Aragoto: "Revival."
[YUKINE]
Meow. Mew-meow!