[YATO]
The entrance to the underworld.
And it's open, so he
must already be inside.
Hey.
Are you sure we'll be able
to get back out once we go in?
Entering the underworld
is like jumping into a vent.
It's basically asking
to get eaten by Phantoms.
[NORA] Phantoms are the
least of our worries.
Or have you forgotten?
This is where Izanami dwells.
She's very different
from other gods, right?
Deathless as she is.
The eternal queen
of the underworld.
As long as life and
death exist, she lives.
If she catches you,
there's no escape.
You'll be stuck in the
underworld for eternity.
Frightening, isn't it?
But don't worry.
You've got me by your
side. I'll protect you.
And if I rescue this conjurer,
you'll give me my freedom,
as promised, right?
[YATO]
Hiki.
I can act as a protective
barrier as well.
Don't tell me that precious
Blessed Vessel of yours
can do this.
[YATO]
Let's go.
Hey there, ladies! Have I
got a sweet deal for you!
I'll pass.
Hear me out, okay?
My uncle gave me a bunch of
free tickets to Capypa Land,
and I was thinking it would
be the perfect chance
to hang out with you-know-who.
Who are you talking about?
Oh! You mean that guy you like.
[YAMA]
Who else?
The joys of adolescence.
[YAMA] So, I need you
guys to come, too.
What do ya say?
You want us with
you on your date?
Actually, it's gonna be
more of a triple date.
[AMI, HIYORI]
A triple date?
Yeah, he's bringing
some friends with him.
So that's where you two
come in. Pretty please?
[AMI]
Mm...
What is it about Capypa Land?
[YATO] Aw! But I wanna go!
I wanna go to Capypa Land!
I wanna! I wanna!
I couldn't say anything then,
but I actually wanna go, too.
[YAMA]
Are you in, Hiyori?
Uh... I don't think I can.
I made plans to go
with someone else.
With who?
[HIYORI]
Uh, with...
Great, then it's decided!
We're going next Sunday.
Huh?
Okay, fine. Count me in.
[YAMA] Youthful escapades,
here we come!
[HIYORI] But I don't wanna
go on a date with someone
I've never even met before.
[YAMA] Don't worry!
We'll be there, too.
It'll be fine.
Hey, Hiyori! Have you
seen Yato late--
[MAYU]
What is it, my lord?
Just let her go. She'll be
much better off this way.
Well. I should be
leaving for the Colloquy.
I'll see you when I return.
I dunno if I'm up for
a date this weekend.
[OKUNINUSHI groans] Wasting my
time with another damn Colloquy!
Didn't we just have one?
I'm a busy god, ya know?
I gotta take my wittle
Inaba for a wabbit walk!
[KOFUKU]
Nushi! I missed you so much!
[screams]
[REGALIA 9A]
It's Lady Ebisu Kofuku!
[REGALIA 9B]
The infamous god of poverty?
[REGALIA 9A]
He's done for.
[DAIKOKU]
Kofuku!
Her enthusiasm can
get the best of her.
As her exemplar, you
should train her better!
And what the
hell're you thinking,
using our names
without permission, huh?
Ebisu and I'll sue the
pants off you, just wait!
Aw, now I wanna
kiss you even more!
Such a big, burly god.
and he's afraid of
little Lady Kofuku.
Poor Okuninushi's
always been like that.
Very superstitious.
Hi, Bisha. Hi, Kazu.
How're you doin'?
[BISHAMON]
We're fine. But I'm surprised.
It's rare to see you here.
Yeah, it is.
Hey, have you seen
Yatty by any chance?
Yato?
That's right.
Since he's become a
resident of Takamagahara,
he should've received
today's summons.
Exactly. That's what we
were hoping for, anyway.
[BISHAMON]
Has something happened?
Seem's Yatty's done
a disappearing act.
He's been in the Lower Realm
for a whole month now.
[KAZUMA]
A month? But what about Yukine?
It's strange.
Yatty was so happy he'd finally
become an official god.
He was even excited
about the Colloquies.
That's why we're here.
Maybe he came, too, you know?
[grunts]
[NORA]
Careful not to make eye contact.
They'll spot you.
Yeah, I know.
[NORA] Do you see that
water? Bathe in it.
Gross!
[NORA]
Endure the stench.
It'll keep the nasty Phantoms
from picking up your scent.
This brings back
memories, doesn't it?
Of all the time
we spent together.
All the things we did.
We were unstoppable.
Together, there was
nothing we feared.
Well, you remember.
[YATO] How many days have
passed on the outside?
I've heard time flows
differently here,
just like in Takamagahara.
Could they have
forgotten me already?
[NORA]
Yato.
[gasps]
[YATO grunting]
[YATO]
A mask. Is the conjurer here?
[YATO grunting]
Ebisu?
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
I've gathered you all here
with good reason. There
has been an important
development regarding
the conjurer.
[gasps]
[GOD 7B] Have you learned
the conjurer's identity?
[GOD 7C]
Who is it?
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI] To change
a Phantom into a puppet,
it must be granted a name.
[GOD 7D]
Giving names to those?
[GOD 9A]
What a terrible thought!
[GOD 9B] It would mean
instant corruption!
[GOD 7A]
Quiet, all of you!
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
As you've said, this conjurer
must endure a great deal.
Which indicates a god.
A highly revered one, at that.
[GODS gasping]
Hey! What the hell
are you doing?
[GOD 7A]
The Seven Gods of Fortune?
No! You're wrong. It isn't us!
What's more, how could
you expose us like this?
Anonymity is guaranteed
at a Colloquy!
Uh-huh!
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Fear not.
I am not implying that
any of you is the conjurer,
but why are there
only six of you here?
[gasps]
[BISHAMON gasps]
[GOD 7A] We've received
a written tip, in fact.
It reads as follows:
"I have witnessed
someone naming Phantoms
in the Lower Realm.
The granter's name is Ebisu."
Liar!
Whoever wrote that
phony tip is full of it!
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI]
Therefore.
Ebisu and Iwami, his
overseer, are under arrest.
[OKUNINUSHI] Ridiculous!
He's on his deathbed!
Leave him alone.
He would never--
[TAKEMIKAZUCHI] His residence
is to be cordoned off
and searched at once.
Furthermore, all his Regalia
are to be interrogated.
[FUKUROKUJU]
Unbelievable!
[GOD 7A]
Given this matter's sensitivity,
we kindly ask that the rest
of the Gods of Fortune
remain here. That will be all.
[EBISU] What are you
doing here, Yato god?
[YATO]
Just what I was wondering.
What brings you
to the underworld?
[EBISU]
Is that Yukine you wield?
No. This is Hiiro.
[NORA]
What a relief.
I was hoping we'd
catch up to you.
Now we can fulfill
Father's request.
You're the conjurer
we were sent to rescue.
[gasps]
Hold on. The old man's
connected to Ebisu?
What old man? I'm lost.
I'm afraid I don't know what the
two of you are talking about.
Is this "old man" you speak
of your father, Yato god?
Hm. Your refusal to answer
only makes me more curious.
And when I'm curious
about something,
I can be very
difficult to deter.
Regrettably, I don't have
time to spend on this now.
Ah. I know.
We can talk further
on the outside.
When would be a
good time for you?
[YATO]
You're missing the point.
I came down here to rescue you.
You came all this
way to rescue me?
Well that's very kind of you.
All right. I've had about
enough of this cesspool.
Let's get outta here.
Hey, where the hell
are you going?
[EBISU]
I can't leave just yet.
The Phantoms have
increased in number.
Don't make eye contact!
Oh, look at that.
There appears to be one
heading right for you.
--[growling]
--[YATO screams] Hiki!
[BULL PHANTOM 9A roars]
Oh, here's another one.
[YATO]
Stop looking at them, will you?
Hey! There's one behind you!
My, that was excellent work.
I can see that you'll come
in very handy down here.
I'm terribly
uncoordinated, you see.
In fact, I can't even
tie my own shoes.
Tell me,
are you any good
with a bow knot?
Well. I'm better
with bondage knots.
Oh? That's very impressive.
Are you for real?
I'm entirely reliant
upon my Regalia.
How rude. I should have
introduced them by now.
Please forgive me.
Kuni. Tatsu. Uta.
You brought your
Regalia with you?
I'm Kunimi.
I'm Tatsumi.
I'm Utami.
Incidentally, Kunimi
ties the best bow knot
you'll ever see.
Next time, let's give these
"bondage knots" a try.
Of course, Young Master.
What's with you people?
It seems the path splits here.
This guy's gonna make
my head explode.
[EBISU grunts]
Young Master!
What is it? What's wrong?
Whoa, hold on! Are you blighted?
It's nothing to worry about.
Guessing it was your conjured
Phantoms that did this.
Unfortunately, my
invocations are still
far from perfect.
For now, I merely control
Phantoms using masks
I've collected. This system
does have its merits, however.
It may sound odd, but there
is a certain satisfaction
in naming and
employing a Phantom
as one would a Regalia.
Although, I must admit that
it has been far from easy.
I am tainted by
each failure, you see.
Masked Ones demand
even greater strength.
They're far beyond
me at present.
Not for much longer, though.
Soon I will have
the necessary power.
[YATO]
You're in bad shape.
We need to get you
out of here soon.
No, thank you.
These Phantoms are nothing.
Not compared to what's ahead.
You don't wanna go
any further, trust me.
Why, because of Izanami?
[EBISU]
She's the reason I'm here.
I came to see Izanami
and get a Locution Brush.
Now if you don't mind,
let's be on our way.
[gasps]
[EBISU, YATO grunt]
Where are we?
[HIYORI chuckles]
I haven't had guests in ages!
Wha--? Hiyori?
Well? Come in, come in!
No! It can't be her.
The woman from the Olive Tavern?
Make yourselves comfortable!
What, are you blind?
That is clearly a
high school girl!
High school girl? You're crazy.
Hey, I see the way you're
looking at her, you old pervert!
The woman from the Olive Tavern
is definitely not
a high school girl.
No mere teenager can make
steaks as good as hers are.
[YATO] What the hell
are you talking about?
Would you care for
some refreshments?
Don't eat or drink
anything here.
If you do, you'll never leave.
Please have some.
There's plenty.
Oh, what's wrong?
Do you not like me?
Don't be shy now,
of course you do!
[grunts]
[HIYORI] You're not alone.
Everybody likes me.
Can I tell you a secret, though?
I think I like you best
of all. Let me show you.
[grunts]
[NORA]
Get away from her!
[EBISU]
Ah, I understand now.
She must alter her appearance
based upon the person
looking at her.
She dons the guise of
someone close to you
to make it easier to
trap you down here.
[YATO] The queen of
the underworld. Izanami.
You should know I
have no intention of
negotiating fairly with her.
That would be a
waste of my time.
Huh?
[YAMA]
Um, hi. I'm Akira Yamashita.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Aimi Tabata.
And I'm Hiyori Iki.
I'm Seki.
My name's Abe.
This girly version
of you is so cute!
So... who is he?
Which one of them's your guy?
He isn't here yet.
[FUJISAKI]
Sorry I'm so late.
Hi. I'm Fujisaki.
[YAMA]
Don't worry about being late.
I'm just glad you could make it.
Really, thanks for coming!
This'll be so fun!
Where would you
like to go first?
I hate waiting in line.
Let's get some Fast Tickets.
Whoa, what's that you've got?
Limited edition
Hundred Archfiends swag!
You've heard of the
Hundred Archfiends?
Uh, yeah! Hasn't
everybody? Hun... dred...
[ABE]
Arch...
[ABE, YAMA]
...fiends!
Uh... So much for
cute and girly!
Any idea what
they're talking about?
[laughs] It's this obscure
band nobody's ever heard of.
[ABE, YAMA] Plenty of people
know who they are!
I'm sorry.
You kinda got
dragged along today.
Oh, no. I'm sorry!
I guess Yama can be
kinda flaky sometimes.
It's okay.
She mentioned you would
be coming, too, so...
Well, where should we start?
I'm a little lost.
I've never been here before.
Heh.
[EBISU]
Lady Izanami.
I was told that I could find
a Locution Brush here.
One that is able
to control Phantoms.
I have come to humbly request
that you give it to me.
[IZANAMI]
How rude.
I'm sure you meant to say
that you came to see me.
You are the second
one to come asking
for a brush, though.
Huh?
These are the
objects in question.
No way...
Enki.
We would like some
tea please, Enki.
[ENKI]
Right away.
[IZANAMI]
I created these myself.
I made them because
I wanted friends.
Friends who wouldn't
leave me. You see...
Everyone who looks upon
my true form leaves.
Always.
You want this badly, don't you?
If I give it to you,
will you be my friend?
[EBISU]
Your friend?
Unfortunately, being
your friend is not
something that I can do.
However--
[EBISU, YATO grunt]
[NORA] Yato. Don't
fight her. I mean it.
She's on an entirely
different level than us.
Not even I am sharp
enough to harm her.
[IZANAMI]
My offer is a simple one.
I will give you
the Locution Brush.
In exchange, one of you will
stay here and be my friend.
That part is up to you.
You should think
hard before deciding.
The agreement will be binding.
I'm sorry it worked
out this way.
[YATO]
Wait, what are you saying?
You're the one who will
remain here in the underworld.
I came for the brush.
I mean to leave with it.
I came to save your ass,
and this is how
you say "thank you"?
[yells]
[EBISU, YATO grunt]
[ALL screaming]
[ALL laughing]
[ABE]
Yay!
[AMI, SEKI giggle]
[FUJISAKI]
Awesome!
I always wanted to
get my photo taken
with one of those.
I know, me, too!
I wanted to get one
with me and, uh, me and...
[KAZUMA]
Restraint!
Borderline!
[YUKINE panting]
[KAZUMA]
Excellent!
[YUKINE]
It's just you!
Hello! Thirsty?
[YUKINE] Quit ambushing
me like that, will you?
It's my version of a pop quiz.
So the Colloquy's over, then?
No, they sent all the
attendants home early
for some reason.
That almost never happens.
Huh. What about Yato?
Was he there?
[KAZUMA]
No.
Okay.
So, Yukine. I heard
Yato's disappeared.
Is that really true?
[YUKINE] Yeah. Apparently,
it happens all the time.
[KAZUMA]
He seems a lot calmer
than I would expect him to be.
I know all too well
how a troubled Regalia
can harm its master.
He's staying calm
for Yato's sake.
You've made great progress.
[YUKINE]
Huh?
Okay, then. Today,
we'll practice Restraints.
[YUKINE]
Great! I'm ready!
[YATO grunts]
[EBISU]
Kunimi is a rare type of Regalia
that can control its
master's movements.
Unarmed combat is his specialty.
[EBISU] Tatsumi and Utami
are very capable, too.
I may not be a god of war,
but I am a god of fortune.
And as such, I have great
confidence in my luck.
Oh.
I hear you reincarnate
all the time.
Sounds real lucky.
[EBISU]
My Masked Ones come at a prince.
They've devoured many of
my previous incarnations.
Tch. You talk about
reincarnating like it's nothing.
Why are so bent on
being a conjurer?
Let me ask you.
Why do you exist, Yato god?
Why are you still here?
I did some research
before I came to visit you.
I like to be informed.
Formally, you're
considered a god of war,
but some stories say
you're a god of calamity.
Those instances aside,
I've only heard
your name in a few
oral traditions.
If you're so close to
vanishing already, then why--?
Stop talking!
I was born from people's
wishes, just like you!
So I don't wanna disappear.
Tell me what's wrong
with that, huh?
I wanted to make them
happy, that's all. Okay?
[grunts]
[pants]
[YATO]
You're not lookin' so good.
That blight must
be pretty painful.
I envy you.
[YATO]
Huh?
The way you care
about your life.
It's not something I've
experienced. Such passion.
You have the determination
that marks a good god.
The kind of god that
can make people happy.
Hurry! You can't take much more.
[grunts]
--[YATO groans]
--[EBISU] It's a mistake
to underestimate my men.
Come, Hi--
[EBISU]
Come, Toki!
[IZANAMI giggles]
That was such an exciting fight.
And it looks like you get to
stay and be my friend, Yato!
I have what I came for.
Shall we go now, Yato god?
Bastard! You planned
this all along?
I did tell you
I had no intention
of negotiating fairly.
And you, Hiiro!
[NORA giggles]
What gives?
You didn't tell me
you served Ebisu, too.
[NORA]
Sorry.
Small world, isn't it?
Kunimi says I named her
five incarnations back.
Is that right, Tsutsumi?
Yes. It's been awhile.
This is sort of an
awkward reunion, isn't it?
I mean, I know you're
a Nora and all,
but this is a lot to take.
It's strange, but I suddenly
feel much closer to you.
Stop! Ew!
You're leaving?
You can't do that.
You were supposed to
stay and be my friend!
We need to hurry.
Hiki!
[YATO]
What are you doing? Come on!
I'm glad I was able to
see you. Goodbye, Mother.
Hold on. Mother?
[IZANAMI] Please don't
leave me! I'm so lonely.
So very lonely. I won't let you.
You'll stay here with
my other friends!
I suspect it would be best
if we got out of here
as quickly as we can.
Uh-huh.
Hiyori and Yukine are
out there waiting for me.
I will make it back to them.
It's so strange.
I feel like I'm close
to remembering something,
but I don't know what it is.
Oh! A Capypa with a crown.
They'll love this little guy!
Of course, they won't
share, so I'll get two.
Or maybe one for
all three of us!
[FUJISAKI] Three for you, too?
They for your family?
No. Actually, they're for...
[heartbeats]
[HIYORI]
They're for... Who?
[heartbeats]
[HIYORI] What's going on?
Something feels wrong.
The parade's starting
in a second.
We should get going.
[HIYORI]
What is it?
I feel like I'm
forgetting something.
Something that's
really important.
Ready? We--
[HIYORI] So many glittering,
colorful lights.
Fireworks flooding the sky.
A sparkling parade procession
illuminating the night.
Even the people's smiles
seem to shine brightly,
giving off a rosy,
cheerful glow.
But to me...
To me it all seems
distant and dull.
The light feels so far away.
It seems like someone's missing.
Someone who should be
next to me, smiling.
Who did I wanna
get a picture with?
Who did I want to give a
present to? Who isn't here?
Or am I wrong?
Am I imagining things?
You okay?
[FUJISAKI gasps]
[HIYORI]
Why? Why can't I remember?
I wanted to come here with him.
To get a picture together.
I... I wanted to stay
by his side, but now...
[EBISU] Oh, dear.
I forgot my hand cream.
[YATO] Hand cream?
That's very dainty of you.
[EBISU] It's very
difficult to count money
with dry fingertips, you know.
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"A Certain Desire."
[YATO]
Yeah, of course I know!
I know all about money!