[BISHAMON] Kazuma. Is there
anything to report?
[KAZUMA]
No activity from the heavens.
We should be the first
to arrive on the scene.
Aiha, listen.
I know we haven't fought
together much lately,
but I'll need your
strength today.
I hope I'm not asking too much.
No! You can count on me.
[KURAHA]
Milady.
Pardon me, but if Lord Ebisu
really is the conjurer,
as the heavens
allege him to be--
It's possible his Masked
Ones attacked our clan.
No, I don't think so.
It isn't the sort of
thing he would do.
He is unconventional,
I'll grant you that.
but he would never disrupt
the heavens without good cause.
I have faith in him as a
fellow God of Fortune.
I won't let him die needlessly.
Let's keep moving.
[KAZUMA, KINUHA, AIHA]
Yes, my lady!
[grunts]
[BISHAMON]
A Vent?
[YUKINE]
A Vent? Now what's going on?
It's been a while,
but if I remember right--
Don't Vents open
into the underworld?
[gasps] Let's go
get a closer look.
This could be our chance
to find a way in.
[HIYORI]
Yato. Please be all right.
[bell jingles]
[YUKINE] Okay, listen,
when we get there--
Where is she?
[HIYORI] I-- I can't move.
I'm being restrained.
[KUGAHA] Oh, my. What a
surprise, meeting you here.
But maybe we've come
on similar errands.
Do you have business to
settle with Yato as well?
[HIYORI]
Kugaha! What's he doing here?
You see, I owe him for this.
Do you know how annoying it is
to live with only one hand?
The simplest tasks
become so difficult.
I mean to change that,
and your hand will do nicely.
[HIYORI]
Yato!
[YUKINE]
Hiyori!
[HIYORI gasps]
You stay the hell away from her!
[YUKINE]
Kugaha! Restraint!
[KUGAHA]
Hm...
[gapss] It didn't work.
Of course it didn't work.
I am not Kuga anymore.
An invocation requires
your target's name.
So it's fairly easy to determine
who has the upper
hand here, Yukine.
What do we do now?
[YUKINE]
You just stay back!
Wait, what?
[laughs] Hear the
shock in her voice?
She's surprised a Blessed
Vessel could be so weak.
[YUKINE gasps]
Say what you want.
You're just a backstabbing Nora.
Whose dog are you this time?
[KUGAHA chuckles]
Listen to the feisty little boy!
You put on a good show,
but I bet you're panicking
because you don't know my name.
I've heard it all before.
Gods and other Regalia are
constantly insulting us Noras.
But do you even know the
real reason why they do it?
Because we Noras
are so powerful.
To use an invocation
against someone,
you must first know their name.
But Noras have multiple names.
You are now experiencing how
unsettling, even terrifying,
that fact can be to those
who aren't like us.
That's why everyone despises us.
Because they hate uncertainty
and fear the unknown.
Because they cannot name
you, they despise you?
Don't listen to him.
He's messing with your head!
[laughs] Understand now,
Blessed Vessel?
Others like you may enjoy
fame and the worship
of many believers, but
they amount to nothing.
Not even Kazuma
can equal my power.
Truth is, the strong are
strong, blessed or not.
Look at little Hiiro.
She's a perfect example.
Who is Hiiro?
You know, the one Yato
always goes back to.
Little lady Hiiro,
dressed in white.
Nora?
You mean you didn't
even know her name?
Did your master keep it
a secret from you? How sad.
And if he took her with
him into the underworld,
he must trust her a lot
more than you, huh?
Shut up!
Yukine!
Really? Let's see
what you've got!
[grunts]
[KUGAHA]
Nope! Not good enough!
[grunting]
[YUKINE]
No way! He's overpowering me!
But I'm a Blessed Vessel!
[YUKINE grunts]
[yelps]
Pathetic. Just pathetic.
[HIYORI]
Hurry! Let's get out of here!
[cackles]
You can't beat a Nora!
Don't let him get to you, okay?
You have to remember!
You're a Blessed Vessel.
Yeah, I know that!
You're the one Yato
made his exemplar.
I know! I know! But still...
He took her! Why not
take me, damn it?
Don't think like that.
Come on, let's play some more!
I'm still having fun!
[YUKINE]
You know how hard I've worked
trying to get stronger.
It's all been for him.
I wanted to make sure
Nora never became
his exemplar instead.
Now this!
[laughing] There's no use
running away, kids!
[HIYORI, YUKINE panting]
He chose Nora.
Look, you should know,
Yato told me something once.
And I knew he meant it. Listen.
He told me he'd always wanted
to find someone like you.
[YATO]
Thank you, Yukine.
As long as I've lived,
you're the first Regalia
to change for me. I'm so gonna
brag to everybody about this.
Don't you get it?
You're Yato's one
special person.
[YUKINE]
His... one special person?
It's the truth! Yukine--
[HIYORI, YUKINE yelp]
[KUGAHA]
I found you!
[HIYORI] You have to listen
to me! Have faith in Yato!
[YUKINE growls]
Borderline!
[KUGAHA gasps]
[KUGAHA groans]
[panting]
Wow! Amazing! You did
it. You beat him!
[YUKINE] Let's go, Hiyori.
Let's find Yato.
[YATO groaning]
Damn it.
[NORA]
Hold on! Stay strong, Yato.
[laughs] I did it.
I actually did it!
I managed to save Ebisu!
And I didn't do it
for my old man.
I did it because I wanted to.
Don't you dare die, Ebisu!
If you give up now, I'll
kick the crap outta you.
Hear me? That's a promise!
[yelps]
[EBISU]
Is this right?
Do all of these names
belong to me? So many.
If you include the local
and historical variants.
[EBISU]
I'm almost like a Nora then.
And it looks like the name Ebisu
has many different meanings.
Including "drowned corpse."
With all these possibilities,
who am I, really?
[IWAMI] One story claims
that you are Master Hiruko,
the first child of Lord
Izanagi and Lady Izanami.
[EBISU]
Hiruko.
[IWAMI]
Yes, that's right.
Though, I now call you
Lord Ebisu because
it is the name you are most
widely known by these days.
I see.
I wonder why my parents
didn't want me.
[BISHAMON]
Ebisu. Ebisu!
Come to your senses!
[KAZUMA]
He's awake!
[BISHAMON]
Are you all right?
[EBISU]
Bishamon.
Thank goodness.
With the way you
were lying there,
I thought you had been executed!
[KAZUMA]
Can you stand, Lord Ebisu?
[YUKINE]
Lady Bishamon! Kazuma!
[KAZUMA]
You two! Why are you here?
I told you to stay away!
Who is that man?
Lord Ebisu.
[groans]
Be careful! You're still weak.
The Yato god.
He didn't make it out.
He's still in the underworld.
[EBISU] The Yato god is
still in the underworld.
You must hurry.
[HIYORI, YUKINE, BISHAMON gasp]
I don't understand.
What would he be doing there?
He came to the
underworld for me.
To bring me back.
I-If we don't help him,
he'll be Izanami's forever.
Hold on! Why would
Yato go save you?
None of this makes any sense.
Bishamon, please
help him. For...
Did he die?
He's passed out, that's all.
[gasps] Over there!
[gasps]
[IZANAMI chuckles]
[BELDAM LADIES cackling]
[IZANAMI]
I've got you! I've got you!
Now, come to me, my dear.
My beautiful, wonderful,
darling, Yato!
[IZANAMI gasps]
[IZANAMI]
No!
Where are you?
[YATO panting]
Will you be all right?
Here, hold on.
Let me wrap this up for you.
There, all better.
You'll be fine now. Right?
Yeah, sure.
I don't know how you're so calm.
We're gonna die down here
if we don't find a Vent.
You realize that, don't you?
Yes. But as long as I'm
with you, I don't mind.
[YATO gasps]
[YATO, NORA giggling]
[YATO] Hiiro's always been
different from other people.
It's like she's
totally fearless.
Nothing seems to faze her.
And as a Regalia, she's
never once tainted me.
Maybe...
[YATO]
Maybe I could stay with her.
[gasps]
[YATO]
Hiki.
[YATO grunts]
What are you planning to do?
I'm gonna find a Vent,
if it kills me.
I will get back to them,
whatever it takes!
[NORA] Even though you might
already be long forgotten?
[YATO]
I have to get out of here.
And cut ties with the old man.
I have to get back to them!
[HIYORI]
Yato!
[IZANAMI]
Found you!
[YATO grunts]
[IZANAMI]
You're mine now!
Yato!
[IZANAMI]
Come to me, my darling. Come.
Please, Lady Bishamon!
How can we get
into the underworld?
[YUKINE] The entrance is
sealed. Now so's the Vent.
[KOFUKU]
It doesn't matter. You can't go.
[HIYORI]
It's Kofuku and Daikoku.
[BISHAMON]
I'm glad you're here.
That's right! Help us!
You can open up a Vent.
You absolutely cannot
go into the underworld.
It's no place for humans.
You'll never leave alive.
[YUKINE]
Lady Bishamon, I beg you.
Please take me
into the underworld!
Do what?
[YUKINE] You must let me
do this. I have to save him.
I'm prepared to risk
my name for my master.
[KOFUKU]
Yukki.
[YUKINE]
Hm?
If you're that determined,
there's only one option.
You must enter the underworld
as someone else's Regalia.
Are you willing
to become a Nora?
[gasps]
He can't do that!
[BISHAMON] There is no need
for you to sully your name,
Blessed Vessel of Yato.
You can leave this to me.
I'll bring back your master.
[YUKINE]
Are you sure?
[BISHAMON]
Kura.
Stay and look after Ebisu.
Yes, my lady.
[BISHAMON] It makes no
difference where he hides.
The heavens will find him.
Hopefully, he will
recover enough to explain
what he's been up to.
We must clear him
of these charges.
Now, let's hurry. Choki!
Right!
[KOFUKU]
Bisha, please save him.
Please get our Yatty back.
I will.
[KOFUKU]
Kokki.
Don't do anything reckless.
We want all of you
back here in one piece!
O band of fiends treading
upon sacred land!
With the Kokki,
I pierce you. Bore!
Let's go!
[KINUHA, AIHA, KAZUMA]
Right!
Lady Kofuku, stand
back where it's safer.
Those fools!
I'm surprised they even
survived down here.
[AIHA yelps] Something just
flew up my skirt. Ew!
Stop it! We need to stay calm.
Why do you suppose Yato
entered the underworld?
Ebisu claims Yato
went there to save him.
I don't know what his
true goal might have been.
But there's one thing
I'm certain of.
The Yato god has people
waiting for him.
So we must make sure he returns.
[FISH PHANTOM 11A growls]
[KAZUMA] Scouting the area.
Follow this waterway.
There's a cave at the end of it.
[BISHAMON] And Yato? Can you
determine his location?
[KAZUMA]
Look at the ground, my lady.
[BISHAMON]
Hm?
[KAZUMA] Do you see a
thread-like substance?
It stretches down
toward the cave.
It's not thread, it's hair!
[KAZUMA] I think we can
assume it belongs to her.
[DAIKOKU]
Whoa. What happened?
I did try to hold back a little,
but even so, no Vent of mine
should close up so quickly.
That last Vent seemed to close
out of nowhere, too.
What's going on here?
Is she sealing up
the underworld?
[panting]
[IZANAMI]
Are you ready to give up
and stay here with me?
My sweet. My Yato.
[IZANAMI]
Huh?
[coughs]
[YATO gasps]
[BISHAMON] You're Izanami,
the queen of the underworld?
[IZANAMI]
Who are you?
One of the Seven
Gods of Fortune.
Bishamonten. I seek
the Yato god.
Will you turn him over?
If not, we fight.
No holding back!
Yeah, you know who
you're up against?
A war god with a Blessed Vessel!
Bishamon? You came?
She's caught him.
[BISHAMON]
There's no way he'll be able
to escape on his own.
Listen, everyone.
Don't even think about
trying to defeat her.
If we're not careful,
we'll be stuck here forever.
The underworld
is Izanami's realm.
We're here for the Yato god.
When we have him,
we leave at once.
[KAZUMA, AIHA, KINUHA]
Right!
[IZANAMI]
How dare you!
I was having a lovely
tea party with my friend.
You interrupted us!
[grunts]
Impressive.
It's no wonder she's known
as the supreme war god.
Still...
[KINUHA gasps]
Nothing happened?
But how is that possible?
A blow that strong
and it did nothing?
We're in big trouble!
Everyone focus!
We all need to
work together now!
[KAZUMA, AIHA, KINUHA]
Right!
Fools! You shouldn't have come.
Hurry! Get outta here!
If you're looking for Ebisu,
he left. I helped him.
He should be safe.
[BISHAMON]
Be quiet! You suicidal maniac!
Don't you want to be rescued?
Rescued? What are you...?
[BISHAMON]
Yato god.
I have hated you to
the core of my being.
I loathed you,
and I loathed myself
for being saved by you.
But whatever I've said before,
you weren't to blame for the
deaths of the Ma and Ha clans.
I have actually
known that all along.
Their deaths were my fault.
Yato god!
I hated you because it was
all I could do to keep going!
In spite of that,
you've saved me twice.
Are you telling me
you came all this way
to say "thank you"?
You're freakin' crazy!
You can say whatever
you want about me,
but I always pay my debts.
That is why I am here!
[yells]
[IZANAMI screams]
You famous gods are
only so brave and daring
because you can reincarnate!
Do not think me so complacent!
I don't wish to die. I'll
fight to remain who I am!
Veena.
Yato god, hear me well!
Your friends await you outside.
Yukine and Hiyori Iki.
[gasps]
[BISHAMON] That's right!
So don't you give up!
[YATO]
They're waiting...
[YATO] Hiyori and Yukine.
They're waiting for me!
[grunting]
[yelling]
My lady, let's try again.
[KOFUKU]
Bore!
[KOFUKU gasps]
It's no use!
The Vent is just
closing right back up.
[DAIKOKU] Damn it!
They won't have a way out!
Please, Milady.
[HIYORI]
Yato.
[KOFUKU]
Bore!
[grunts]
Yato.
[EBISU] A Blessed Vessel
and a human girl.
I see. They are his purpose.
They are why he keeps fighting.
He's awoken!
[KOFUKU]
Ebi! Are you okay?
You can help Yato.
If you wish to bring him
back from the underworld,
there's a way.
[BOTH gasp]
However, not just
anyone will do.
It requires a human.
[KAZUMA]
Hm.
[BISHAMON]
What's wrong, Kazuma?
[KAZUMA]
I can't decide if your bath
should be 105 or 106 degrees.
[BISHAMON]
On the next Noragami Aragoto:
"Your Voice Calls Out."
[KAZUMA]
What do you think?
[BISHAMON] Honestly? I don't
much care either way.