There we go.
Well, that the last of it.
Are you sure you haven't
forgotten anything?
Oh, well lemme just make sure.
Oh, thanks!
Chi!
Shinbo decided to move out so he
and Miss Shimizu
could live together.
Well, we've pretty much
got everything, I'd say.
The whole kidnapping
incident's over now,
and things are back to normal.
I still go to prep school,
and I still work at
the pub, My Pleasure.
But even though everything
looks the same as before,
something just seems a
little different somehow.
Chi's gone back
to work at Tirol.
And she looks as happy as usual,
as if nothing had ever happened.
As if nothing had ever happened.
Hey, Motosuwa!
Is anything wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry,
that looks like it!
Okay, that does it.
Thanks a lot for all the help.
Well then Motosuwa,
see ya 'round.
Sure, I'll see you at school.
Yeah, something is different.
Something, enough to make me
want to find out more, I guess.
Excuse me, but why did you
put your hand on my head?!
So Sumomo and Kotoko
are the same size?
Aye! Sumomo's
16 centimeters tall!
That's not what I asked!
Oh, hi, this is Motosuwa.
I was just sort of wondering
how everything's going.
Yeah, I guess so.
Okay, I'll head on over. See ya.
Hideki, going out?
Yeah, I am.
You wanna come with me, Chi?
Chi will go with you!
So, Chi...
Chi?
I was wondering,
do you enjoy working?
Chi enjoys working.
What's so fun about it?
Chi works, Hideki is happy.
No, that's not what I meant.
You know, like the
stuff you do there;
do you have fun doing it?
Chi prefers now more than work.
Huh?
Together with Hideki.
Chi has fun.
I see. Well, it's still
sorta strange to me.
Even now, I just really don't
know that much about Persocoms.
But as far as I can see,
their owners really do seem
to be something
very special to them.
Or maybe it's just
that she was programmed
to be that way by
her previous owner.
Chi?
This must be the destination!
This is the place!
This address is registered
in Sumomo's map data!
Is this correct?
Yeah.
This is Mr. Minoru
Kokubunji's house!
Yes?
Welcome, Mr. Motosuwa.
Oh, hello there, Yuzuki.
Please come in.
This place amazes me every time.
Mr. Motosuwa.
I'm afraid we're
all busy right now,
so there's nobody
free to greet you.
Sorry about that.
But would you be so kind
to join me in my study?
Uh, sure.
Amazing.
A PA system in a house.
Oh, and please watch your step.
Huh?
What's this?
What are they doing?
They must be doing research.
Research.
Please come in.
Hey.
Sorry to bug you
when you're so busy.
That's all right. I see
you brought Miss Chi.
Yeah, I was a little concerned
about leaving her at home alone.
Has anything else happened?
Oh, no, not at all;
nothing like that.
I see. Well, I'm glad.
I think I'll take
a short break now.
You should rest, too, Yuzuki.
Thank you.
I've put together all my
research so far about Miss Chi.
I'm still working on it, though.
Oh, thank you.
I don't suppose you have a
quieter way to wait, do you?
Nope. This is how
I was programmed!
Even after all this,
I still don't have any idea
what kind of Persocom Chi is.
Until now, I didn't really
think it was such a big deal.
But someday,
if something like that
or even worse were to
ever happen to Chi again,
I wouldn't be able to
do anything about it.
I need to know.
I want to find out as
much as I possibly can.
If there's anything
I can do for you,
I'd be happy to help.
And about the contents
of this envelope...
From what I've pieced together
there seems to have
been a very hidden side
to the development
of the "chobits" series.
Hidden?
Well, this goes deep in
the realm of Urban Legend,
so try to keep that in mind.
Intriguing story, though.
"Chobits," said to be
the ultimate Persocoms,
are also supposedly influenced
by a certain syndicate.
When Persocoms were
first being created,
it seems that there was
some sort of a disagreement
between the developers
of the Persocom
and their client, the syndicate.
The constant interference
from the syndicate
apparently made the developers
more and more irritated.
As a result,
unbeknownst to the syndicate,
the developers created
a special Persocom.
And that's--
"Chobits"?
That's right.
And from what
I can tell, it's serious,
because the existence
of "chobits" puts
the syndicate at a
severe disadvantage.
So then, what's
their real purpose?
Well, I haven't gotten that far.
I see.
I'm sorry, Motosuwa.
Huh?
Oh, you don't have
to apologize, Minoru.
You've been incredibly
helpful since all this started.
Nevertheless, the fact remains
that it was my carelessness that
got her kidnapped the other day.
So please allow me
to do whatever I can do
to help you, Motosuwa.
Minoru.
Well, no, actually,
I'd like two of you to be more-
Yuzuki!
I brought you some tea.
Why are you serving the tea?
The maid Persocom is currently
being used by the system.
What are you talking about?
Yuzuki, you're the center
of that system, aren't you?
Why don't you sit
down and take a rest?
I'm sure you're very
tired from all this.
Lord Minoru,
thank you very much.
I can handle this on my own;
I want you to try to relax.
Huh?
Minoru!
Lord Minoru?! Lord Minoru?!
Well, I'm glad to know
that all he really needs
is a good night sleep.
But to be so exhausted that
he'd just collapse like that...
Does that mean he hasn't
been getting any sleep lately?
Yes.
It must be because
of all the research
that I asked him to do for me.
Please, Mr. Motosuwa;
it isn't your fault.
I'm afraid that I'm just
not powerful enough.
Don't say that!
There's no denying that if my
processing speed were faster,
I wouldn't have put Lord Minoru
under such extreme stress.
If only I was just...
more useful.
Miss Yuzuki.
If only there was some
way for me to do something.
Where there's a will,
there's a way.
Kojima?! What're you...?!
Boy, you've got a
lot of nerve, doncha?!
You creep!!
That hurt.
What the heck do you think
you're doing here? Huh?
Hey! Hold on a second, man!
"M" just wanted to borrow
my Persocoms, that's all!
"M"?
Yes, it's true:
Lord Minoru asked for
some help with the research.
Mr. Kojima not only owns them,
but has a lot of
knowledge about Persocoms.
And I really do feel bad
about what I did the other day.
My curiosity just
got out of control.
So I'm helping out to
try to make up for it.
Oh yeah?
And how are you going to that?
Well, you've heard
about the syndicate
that was involved
in the development
of the "chobits" series,
haven't you?
What about it?!
If you really
wanted to find out,
the easiest way is to hack
directly into the syndicate's
main computer and
have a look around.
Hack into the...
And just what are
you trying to say?!
Do ya hafta get so upset?!
Hacking is a term, which means
to find your way
through security systems
and illegally enter a computer
without access privileges.
That's right, it basically means
that you're tapping into
someone else's computer.
Can you really do
something like that?
Absolutely.
At least we know who it
is that we're dealing with.
Then again, there's
always gonna be risks.
Risks? Like what?
We're not dealing
with an ordinary server.
There will definitely be
a lot of security walls
to get through.
You never know, they might
bring on a full system crash.
Wait, a crash is just...
It's when data gets lost, the
memory gets wiped out, you know.
And if it's really bad, the hard
drive can actually be destroyed.
Yeah, well that
sounds pretty awful!
You want to put Miss Yuzuki
through something like that?!
Hey, did I say that?! Come on.
Actually, "M" was
totally against it.
Lord Minoru was?
Yeah, it's true, When I
suggested that he just oughta
take a chance and
let Yuzuki hack into it,
he just suddenly...
Don't you ever say that again!
I won't let it go next time.
Well, nothing else is
gonna be as effective.
I know that!
I'm aware of that.
But I will never let
Yuzuki take that risk.
Lord Minoru.
I never expected that reaction.
It just wasn't like him.
I mean, "M" is usually
the first one to jump
at an opportunity for a
new piece of information.
It makes sense to me.
Miss Yuzuki is a lot more than
just another Persocom to Minoru.
So now, since we
can't go with that plan,
we're using methods that just
aren't getting us anywhere.
He's bound to end up
stressing himself right
over the edge at this rate.
Well to take some of
the strain off Minoru,
I suggest that you do your best
to figure out something else.
Got that?!
Huh?
You've gonna work twice,
no, three times as hard!
And I'm gonna be watching you,
so don't try to slack off!
I think we'll stay here tonight.
I'm still a bit worried
about Minoru anyway.
Hey, come on, man!
All right, so which
room are you working in?
Okay, okay, whatever
you say, just let go of me!
He's sleeping.
Back to work!
Don't forget, you were the
one who programmed me
so I wouldn't be able to
speak anything but the truth.
Yeah, I know. I'm working!
Kotoko. That's right, most
Persocoms don't tell lies.
That's because they
were programmed that way.
So then, when Miss Yuzuki...?
If only I was
just more useful...
So if that's the truth,
then there's something...
Miss Chi.
Hideki said to
check how things are.
Everything's fine
just at the moment.
Yuzuki?
That's Lord Minoru
with his elder sister.
Elder sister? Not Yuzuki?
That's right. I am different
from his elder sister.
I was made to be just like her,
and I've been programmed
with a great deal of
data about her, too.
But I am simply not her.
His real elder sister would've
been much more helpful to
Lord Minoru, I'm afraid.
Miss Chi, tell me:
if you knew that you needed
to help Mr. Motosuwa,
would you do
anything for him?
Anything for him?
For example,
would you do something
even if it could possibly
cause you to break?
Chi is always glad
when Hideki is happy.
If it made Hideki happy,
Chi would!
Yuzuki?
What the...?
What's with the Persocoms?
If the power keeps
fluctuating like that,
it could cause problems
with our operation.
All right, let's
see what's going on
with the house security system.
Hm?
What's wrong?
That's strange.
All the power in the house
is concentrated in one spot.
Looks like there's
someone using the system
in the study right now.
The study? Minoru's?
Hm?
All right, who's that
so late at night?
Someone's trying to get in.
Yeah.
Well, well, this is interesting:
someone's breaking
through my security system.
Whatta ya think? Is it her?
Nah, although I gotta admit it;
it's a pretty good Persocom.
I'm connecting.
Minoru! Are you in there?
Come on, the doctor
told you to take it easy!
What's going on?
Minoru?!
Huh? Then who's in the study?
I don't know; I'm the only one
who can use the system
in there, except...
Yuzuki! I know you're
in there; answer me!
Huh?
Yuzuki! Open the door!
Lord Minoru.
Yuzuki! What are you doing?!
Open this door!
Why would Yuzuki do something
like this without telling him?
Lord Minoru.
Miss Yuzuki?!
She's tied to the PA system.
Mr. Kojima said that
it might be possible
to hack into the
syndicate's server.
I am attempting to do so.
I am currently deciphering
the fifth password.
Yuzuki, as soon as
you crack the password,
the Security program
will kick in,
and you'll be targeted
immediately!
You see, I wasn't
able to understand
how you felt, Lord Minoru.
Yuzuki?
Even though you knew
this was the best way,
you were concerned about me,
and took it all upon
your own shoulders.
But, I'm sure that
your real elder sister
would have understood
completely.
What are you
talking about, Yuzuki?
Why are you doing this?
That's right, why would you
believe something like that?
Is it because you're
programmed with her data?
You believe it doesn't matter
what might happen to you,
as long as you do what
his sister would have done?
Is that how she's
been programmed?
It just doesn't
seem right somehow.
I just want to be
helpful to Lord Minoru,
like his elder sister was.
No, Yuzuki; it's not the same.
It's not the same!
You're not my sister, Yuzuki!
Decryption complete.
Commencing data download.
Yuzuki, no!
The lock!
Yuzuki!
Yuzuki! Yuzuki!
Boy, that's a rough
way to send 'em off.
I have no sympathy for anyone
who tries to enter Zima.
Why, if I didn't know better,
I'd say you sound
a little bit jealous.
Except that we're
Persocoms, of course.
Yuzuki.
You're awake.
Lord Minoru. Everyone.
No, don't get up.
Okay, I'm done with the tests.
It doesn't look like there was
any serious damage done to her.
That's good.
You gave us a real
shock, Miss Yuzuki.
You're pretty lucky this cable
burnt through as fast as it did.
I'm sorry to worry
you all like this.
I'll do a self-scan now.
Lord Minoru,
Yes?
I'm afraid some data
was lost in the crash.
Data about your elder sister.
Minoru.
Could you please
re-enter the data
that pertains to your sister?
Anything else?
Huh?
It seems the rest of
my memories appearsto be fine.
I see.
Well, I won't enter
any data about her.
Huh?
When my sister died,
I wasn't able to
bring myself to accept it.
Actually, I didn't
want to accept it.
And that's why,
I made you, Yuzuki.
I tried to make you as much
like her as I could remember,
but you're not
my older sister, Yuzuki.
I'm terribly sorry, it's
because I'm not good enough.
That's not true.
Nobody could ever realy
take my sister's place.
And believe me, nobody
could replace you either.
Nobody could ever replace me?
That's right.
That can't be true;
I'm a Persocom.
Yes, but I could never think of
another Persocom the way
I think of you, Yuzuki.
And it doesn't
make any difference
that it's all
been programmed in.
Yuzuki is Yuzuki.
So I won't be entering any
more data about my sister.
The time I spent with
my sister is something
I'm sure I'll always
cherish deep in my heart.
But the times I've
spent with you, Yuzuki,
are very precious memories, too.
And that's why I want to
go right on making them.
Not as a replacement
for my sister.
I wanna spend time with you.
With Yuzuki.
I can stay by your side,
Lord Minoru,
even if I cannot be a
replacement for your sister?
That's exactly what
I'm trying to say,
Yuzuki: I want you by my side.
Lord Minoru.
Oh boy, how did it get
to be morning already?
Yuzuki.
Huh?
Yuzuki looked happy.
Yeah, she did.
Chi is happy too.
Hm?
Hideki, what are memories?
Oh, well, let's see...
They're special things that live
deep within the heart. I guess.
I mean, they're
really not like data;
you can't just replace
or reenter them.
Do Chi and Hideki have memories?
Oh, yeah!
Chi!
Things that can't easily
be reentered or replaced...
They're something... different.
Mr. Motosuwa.
Oh hi, Minoru,
is everything all right?
I'm sorry to have
troubled you with all this.
No, no, please don't apologize.
I'm the one who
asked for your help.
Don't worry about it.
I'll keep up the investigation.
Thank you.
But try not to get too
stressed out over it, okay?
I'll try.
This might help.
Huh?
It's a compilation of the data
that Yuzuki managed to download.
Oh, I see.
I haven't had time to do more
than just skim over most of it,
but it's a list of the people
who developed the Persocom.
There was a picture that
may very well surprise you.
Miss Hibiya! Miss Hibiya!
Where could she be?
My guess is that she was
one of the main people
on the development team.
But, now I really
don't understand.
Miss Hibiya!
Hideki, when do you feel happy?
Let's see...
Well, when I eat a
really delicious meal.
Or when I get a good score
on a prep school exam
And, I guess, well, uh...
When you hold hands?
Well, yeah, I feel happy
when I hold hands, I guess.
But why are you
asking me that, Chi?
Chi.
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Wears, Then Takes Off."
Everyone is happy
when they hold hands!
Chi!