Omigod, look,
he's out there again!
Every day for
the past two weeks!
He just stands out there
panting! It's frightening.
Mommy, why is the
man breathing like that?
Shhh! Don't look at him!
All right!
Today's the day
I finally go in there!
I just can't do it!
Why can't I just say
"Can I have some underwear?"
I couldn't buy them
again today, after all.
What am I doing?
I'm home.
Ah! What are you doing
in that kind of pose, Chi?
Hideki.
Welcome home.
Yes, I'm home, Chi.
Well, it looks like you've
remembered my name now.
"Hideki" is Hideki's name.
Chi can remember.
Great job, Chi.
You're really talking
well now, aren't ya?
But, uh, well, why were
you getting undressed?
That.
Huh?
The manager brought.
I see, so you were trying
to change into that, huh?
I'll have to go and
say thank you later.
But the problem right now
is we've got to get
you some underwear.
Asking for a dress or
a blouse is one thing,
but I don't know
about underwear.
"Miss Hibiya, do you mind
if we borrow your underpants?"
Ah! I couldn't ask her
for something like underpants!
She'd think I was
a complete pervert
without a doubt!
Pervert?
So it's underpants you're
interested in, eh, Hideki?
Shinbo, couldn't ya
make an effort to knock?!
I did, but you were too busy
yelling "underpants" to hear me!
Oh man, don't tell me
I was saying that out loud?
Shouting's more like it.
So what you're saying is you're
too embarrassed
to buy underpants.
Well I get this strange
feeling every time
I get near the lingerie store.
It's a feeling that
men aren't welcome,
and when I even get
within 20 feet of it- Oh!
It's just no good.
I've really got to
do something about this,
and I've gotta do it soon.
Okay then, how about
if you just let Chi go out
and buy some for herself?
Huh?
There's no way I can let
Chi go out all by herself!
She doesn't know
her way around town!
Hey, don't sweat it, buddy.
I can just let
you borrow Sumomo.
Huh?
Aye!
She's got GPS navigational
software installed.
You just give her a destination,
and she'll map out the route.
Sumomo can handle all that?!
That's so awesome!
Chi?
Would you like to go shopping?
Go shopping?
Yeah. So you can
get some underpants.
Underpants?
All right, Chi. Look.
This.
You're going to go
find this and buy it.
Bait?
Ah! No, Chi, you are
not going to go buy bait.
Look!
What I'm talking about is
what this person is wearing!
This, or this, or this!
Understand?
These are underpants.
Underpants.
Hideki wants this?
Yeah, this is exactly
what I want, Chi!
Do you think you
can remember it?
Chi can remember.
Gah!
Good morning!
According to schedule,
it's time for wakie exercises!
And we finish off
with a deep breath!
All right, well done!
Uh?
What was all that?!
Oh, scary!
I can't believe that
Shinbo actually gets up
to this every single morning.
In any case, Sumomo,
today you take
care of Chi, alright?
Of course!
Take care of yourself.
No, see today, I say
"take care of yourself",
you say "I'll be going now."
I'll be going now.
That's right.
Don't take any dark alleyways.
Always keep your eyes open,
and make sure you
never follow strangers!
And remember to look both ways
before you cross the street!
Dark alleyways. Follow
strangers. Cross street.
Alright then, now one last time.
Tell me what are you going to
be saying to the salesclerk?
"Underpants thank you please."
That's right!
And you give the
clerk money your money
for the underpants?
Do you understand?
Chi understands.
I'll be going now.
I hope she'll be okay.
Huh? Oh my, are you going out
somewhere all by
yourself today, Chi?
Chi is going
shopping with Sumomo.
Well isn't that just wonderful!
Please do be careful, though.
I'll be going now.
Initiating navigational program!
Turn left then go straight!
Wave those arms and legs,
and let's be
cheerful on our way!
Underpants,
underpants, underpants.
Underpants...
Prepare to turn right
at next corner! Turn!
Underpants,
underpants, underpants...
Hey, Hideki, are you
worried about something?
Yeah. I wonder if she's
doing everything right.
Right about what?
Well the underpants, of course.
Underpants?
Yeah, underpants. Underpants!
Huh??!
Umm, it's great
weather today, huh?
Yeah, nice days like
this really make me
wanna go outside and
have some fun, too!
Isn't that true?
I was just thinking
the same thing!
The problem's on page 15.
Right.
Underpants, underpants,
underpants.
Make a left turn now!
We must stop here for a moment,
as we prepare
to cross the street!
Bicycle.
Ding-dong! That's right!
You're correct!
Traffic light.
Ding-dong! Correct again!
Crosswalk.
Ding-dong-ding-dong!
Absolutely correct!
Chi.
Underpants.
The light is green!
Let's raise our arm
as we cross the street!
Warning! Warning!
You have strayed
from the correct route.
Please return to
the original path!
Can it be, that Chi...?
What is it?
I've got a bad feeling
about things. Uh?
Since you're up,
you can start on page 21.
Right.
Underpants.
Warning, warning!
This is not a lingerie store!
But this is what
Hideki showed Chi.
This is only advertising!
This is not where you buy it!
Chi can't buy underpants here?
Aye!
Now, let's get back
onto the proper route.
Please turn around!
Underpants.
Ding-dong! You are correct!
Man, I hate this wind.
Hm?
Underpants.
Huh?
Underpants, thank you please.
What are you doing?!
Warning, warning, warning!
This is not a
lingerie store, either!
But, underpants...
You are unable to
buy underpants here.
Please go back exactly
forty feet and turn left!
Underpants.
What's up with that?
Weird Persocom.
I'm so worried about Chi.
Was she able to buy
the underpants or not?
Underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants!
Oh, I knew I should
have gone with her!
For now, why don't
you just try staying here
with us on page 23.
Right.
Chi.
Underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants,
underpants...
Please proceed
straight another 100 feet!
Underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants,
underpants,
underpants, underpants.
Stop now! All traffic halt!
Kitty.
Ding-dong! You are correct!
We must wait until they're
done crossing the street!
Underpants?
Underpants.
Warning, warning! This is
not the correct route!
Warning, warning!
Please return to the
original route at once!
Chi.
No, not underpants.
Chi? Sumomo?
Emergency! Emergency!
Persocom in
life-or-death crisis!
Chi! Where have you gone?
We have big trouble!
Chi is missing!
Emergency! Emergency!
Oh, there-
Big trouble!
The situation is not
turning out as it should!
Sumomo is not a doggie chew-toy!
Chi.
Chi!
Please help Sumomo get free!
Chi.
Hey! Pesu, come on! Let's go!
That was a very close call.
Hey!
I already said
Sumomo is not a chew toy!
It looks like they're
not at the store.
Have they even arrived yet?
Why don't we eat
over at that fountain?
Um... Excuse me, please.
Have you seen a Persocom
with ears like this,
and a mobile unit
about this size,
trying to buy underpants?
Could this guy be the owner
of that Persocom
that acted so weird?
Huh? What? But I, uh-
Don't talk to him!
Who knows what he'll
have his Persocom do next!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Uh, what's the matter with them?
I wonder why they wouldn't
tell me anything.
Could it be that Chi did
something to them?
Guess who!
Oh! I'm so sorry!
Yumi, is that you?
I'm sorry about that.
I really just wanted
to have a little fun.
Are you gonna
be alright, Senpai?
Whoa!
Omigod. Those breasts.
Her breasts.
Hmm? Motosuwa-senpai?
That feeling I just
had was really soft
and warm, you know?
It'd be pretty bad if
breasts were hard and cold.
Wah! No-no-no-no-no-no!!
I was talking to
myself again, wasn't I?
Anyway, what are
you doing down here
in the marketplace, senpai?
Oh, that's right!
I was looking for Chi!
I'm sorry, Yumi,
I'll see you later, okay?
Uh, Senpai!
Chi, where did you
disappear to? Huh?
Chi.
Chi! Chi!
Hideki says to use the crosswalk
when crossing the street.
That's wonderful!
Look both ways, raise your arm
and cross the street.
Very good!
You remembered everything, Chi.
Ah!
You jerk!
What are you standing
in the street for?!
S-Sorry!
Underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants...
Aye! That's the correct route!
Underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants...
Underpants. Bait for Hideki!
Gah!
Just what does she
think she's doing?
Although, it's true it
can be considered bait.
Underpants!
Warning, warning!
That is only another
advertisement!
The store's over there.
Chi.
Underpants, underpants.
No wonder they're late!
They've must've been distracted
by every advertisement in town.
I hope they get to the
store while it's still open.
Underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants.
Underpants!
Warning!
Underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants.
Looks like they'll be all right.
You're almost at the store.
You can do it, Chi.
Underpants,
underpants, underpants,
underpants, underpants.
And stop!
Congratulations!
You have arrived
at the destination!
Ding-ding-ding-ding-ding,
woo-woo, yay!
We can buy underpants here?
Yes! You can! You can! You can!
You can! You can!
Oh yeah, Chi,
that's the way to go!
Now, the only thing you
have to do is tell
the clerk the phrase you
learned this morning.
Chi buys underpants.
Attention please!
Starting right now is our
Super Sale on lingerie!
Everything on the
cart is half price,
all underwear 50 percent
off! Come on in!
Chi!
Oh! This is way too scary!
We must get out
of here, immediately!
Oh Chi, are you
alright in there?
If I help you,
everyone will see!
But I just gotta do it!
Chi! Are you okay?!
Chi!
Huh? Ah! Underpants!
Someone help!
Huh?!
It's the pervert, the one
who's been standing there
staring at the store
all day long every day!
I should have known
we should have tried
to keep an eye on that guy.
Look, it's a misunderstanding!
I can explain it!
Yeah, I just bet you can, pal.
Come on with us.
Huh? No wait,
I haven't done anything!
I'm innocent!
I'm innocent, I can explain!
Chi.
Oh boy, that was very dangerous.
Chi?
Underpants. Gone.
Underpants.
Huh?
Underpants, thank you please.
Oh, what a terrible mess
that was back there.
Why did everybody treat me
like some kind of
pervert or something.
Poor Chi.
It had to be awful for her too.
I sure hope she
got home all right.
I'm back.
Hideki, welcome home!
Chi! You made it back home.
I was so worried about you.
So!
Did you buy manage
to buy some underpants?
Chi.
Did you really get them?
Well, let's see.
This.
But those're men's underwear.
Wait a minute, Chi.
Did you say the words
I told you to say?
Chi told sales clerk:
"Underpants, thank you please,"
because Hideki says
"he wants this."
And, this is what they gave you?
Oh. Well, now I understand.
These underpants are no good?
Thanks for trying, Chi
I know you did your best.
Chi.
That means I have
to go back there.
Oh, Lord, please help me.
Chi?
All right! I'm going in!
Underpants, thank you please!
Hideki, welcome home.
Those clerks at the lingerie
store think I'm a real pervert!
They backed away from me like
I was going to attack
them or something!
It was even worse
than it was yesterday!
Chi.
And on top of that,
I just realized I could
have bought these at
the convenience store!
I'm such an idiot!
Because of these underpants,
because of underwear in general,
I'm now a total pervert!
Pervert?
Hideki is a pervert!
Huh?!
Pervert! Hideki is a pervert!
No, no, don't say that, Chi!
Pervert, pervert!
Ah!
Chi, this is a bookstore.
Chi?
And this is a book.
Books are like data storage,
educational tools.
Books.
Yup. And this math book is much
too expensive for me to buy.
This study guide is also too
expensive for me to buy.
This dictionary? Forget it.
Chi understands.
Oh?
Hideki is dirt poor!
Chobits, next episode:
"Chi Finds."
Dirt Poor!
Dirt Poor.