My name is Hideki Motosuwa.
I'll be turning 19 this year.
Right now, I'm still 18.
This spring,
I'm planning on moving
to Tokyo and going to college!
Oh! There it is!
I'm going to be a
freshman in college!
At least, that's what I thought.
I got rejected!
I failed!
I'm going to be
a bum for a year!
That's it, I'm going
to prep school!
I'll study hard, and make sure
that I get into
college next year!
That's right,
if I'm going to go,
I'll go to Tokyo!
Well, the college I want
to go to is in Tokyo, right?
All right!
I'm gonna go to Tokyo!
I'm finally here.
Tokyo really is a busy city,
just like I thought.
Now, where's my apartment?
It will take
approximately 45 minutes
to arrive at your destination.
You will then need to
switch trains at Ikebukuro.
It's a real Persocom!
Wow, this is the first time
I've seen one in real life!
Lately the whole world has been
talking about IT
and the Internet,
and how advanced it's getting.
It seems like it's
making the world
an easier place to live in.
The most amazing things
are these Persocoms.
They make them look
just like people!
I don't really
know much about it,
but I guess they can
do all kinds of things!
In the small town
where I come from,
out in the country, no one
has a computer like this!
They're so nice!
So cool! I want one!
I really want one!
Are you kidding?!
There's no way
I could afford one!
Uh...
It must be some
kind of performance.
What a strange guy...
Well it is spring...
Mommy I'm scared!
Just don't look
him in the eye dear!
Man, that was embarrassing!
I've really gotta stop
talking to myself in public.
Up until now, the only
things I've ever talked
to were horses and cows.
Boy, those Persocoms sure
do look like real humans.
And, they're pretty cute too!
But man, they're so expensive.
I guess that's okay for
most people, though, huh?
I mean, does everyone out here
in the city have tons
of money or something?
I guess poor college
students-in-training
aren't allowed to
buy them. Is that it?
Ah, darn it all!
I wanna get my own computer!
I wanna send e-mail, too!
And more than anything
I wanna see those
internet porn sites!!
Porn-sites?
Um, uh, no, well I--
What did I say in front
of this pretty girl?
Oh excuse me,
you see I was just trying
to find an apartment.
But I'm not really
sure where it is.
Maybe you've heard of it?
It's called the "Cub Jogasaki."
It's kind of a weird name.
I believe this is the place!
Ahh!
This apartment building's
called the Gub Jogasaki.
Oh! I see.
What?!
You must be Hideki Motosuwa.
Uh,Yes.
My name is Chitose Hibiya.
I'm the manager
of this building.
This is your apartment.
Oh.
The hot water and the
gas line are already set up.
And the circuit breakers
are over here.
Boy, it's a lot
smaller than I expected.
But I can't complain
it's all I can afford.
I put the boxes you sent
in your room for you.
I hope you don't mind?
No! Not at all! Thanks a lot!
I, just hope they
weren't too heavy
for you to carry all
the way up by yourself.
I'm really sorry about that.
It was no trouble at all.
Mr. Shinbo carried
everything up for me.
Uh, Mr. Shinbo?
Yes, he should be
back any moment now.
He's your next door neighbor.
He seems like a very
nice man, in room 204.
Oh I see.
I'll be sure to thank
him when I see him.
Well, it was a pleasure
to meet you Mr. Motosuwa.
The pleasure is all mine!
Thank you! Thank you.
How lucky am I
to have such a
beautiful manager?!
She said that she
lives in apartment 101.
Who knew I would
end up living in a place
right above a
pretty girl like her?
Huh? Okay, be right there!
Maybe it's her again.
Hello!
Huh?
Congratulations!
Congratulations on
your new apartment!
What is that?!
Master, that guy's really scary!
Hey sorry about that man.
I didn't mean
to catch you off guard.
Well, I, uh...
Hey, we haven't
been introduced yet -
I'm Hiromu Shinbo.
I live in the unit
right next door
to yours in number 204.
Oh!
You're the guy who
carried my stuff up here.
That's right!
Thank you very much!
I appreciate it Mr. Shinbo!
What's with all
the formal stuff?
Call me Shinbo!
So, how old are you?
I'm eighteen.
So am I!
You're eighteen, too?
And tomorrow you're gonna
start Seki Prep School, right?
Um, yeah.
Well, I am too!
Losers club!
Hey! Really?!
Absolutely. Nice to meet ya!
So what is this thing?
Oh! That's my Persocom.
It's so small!
Well, it's a mobile unit.
Oh, I see.
Introduce yourself.
Aye!
I am Sumomo!
It's nice to meet you!
Wow she's amazing!!
Whoa, he's scary!
What's the big deal?
Haven't you seen one before?
You don't have
a mobile Persocom?
I wish!
I haven't got a Persocom at all.
You're kidding?!
That's kinda weird.
And even if I did buy one
I wouldn't know how to use it.
It's no big mystery.
Once you turn the switch,
they do the rest.
The OS takes care
of everything after that.
Ah! You're an expert
with these things.
Not really.
So can you do
everything with it?!
Yeah, sure!
I can get my phone calls,
go on the internet
and get all my e-mail.
Really? The Internet too?!
Oh yeah!
And porno sites too, of course!
Really? It can even
access porno sites?
Come on, porno sites
are the basics!
Porno sites! Porno sites!
Shall I warm that up for you?
Uh, yes please.
Right away, sir.
And when it's done,
I will call you.
Please have a
seat while you wait.
A-alright.
Thank you very much, sir!
Have a good evening!
Those Persocoms
really are amazing.
They can even
run cash registers.
Shinbo called his
Persocom Sumomo.
I didn't even know there
were such incredible machines!
He said he could make
phone calls with it.
Man, that's cool!
I doubt I'll ever be able
to afford one, though.
And even if I did have one,
I wouldn't know where to begin.
I don't know anything
about Persocoms.
But I've gotta check out
those porno sites someday.
Persocoms are cool.
They're shaped exactly
like real people.
I only wish I could find
a really cute one
lying around somewhere.
Course that'll never happen.
Oh my god it's a dead body!!
What am I gonna do?!
It must be a murder!
I can't believe it!
My first day in Tokyo, and here
I am at the scene of a crime!
What should I do?!
Okay, don't panic - let's see.
First I should call the police.
Or maybe I should
call an ambulance?
She has those-ears.
There're just like
the ears I saw
in the window at
the electronics store.
Phew!
So that's what she is.
And here I was thinking
it was some kind
of hideous murder or something.
Oh man!
Well, I gotta get back to my
apartment and get organized.
Wait a minute!
This is a Persocom.
And it was left out
here in the trash.
Which means that technically,
this is actually garbage.
And no one wants it,
so I can take it, right?
Right? Right?
Actually I would be
doing a good thing
for the environment
if I were to recycle her.
All that industrial
waste and dioxin.
We don't want more
holes in the ozone layer.
This is heavier than I thought.
This is how much
a Persocom weighs?!
Come on. You have to be kidding!
I'm gonna get squashed to death!
Oh man, I had no idea that's
how heavy computers
were supposed to be.
Well, I guess that's
what they mean
when they say "Heavy
then light upon booting"...
Shinbo said handling these
Persocoms would be easy.
Mobile units must be lighter.
It's amazing!
She's really no different
looking than a human girl.
She's pretty, too.
And soft.
Maybe that's just because
she's still brand new?
Or maybe she was thrown away
because a new model came out?
What a waste of money!
I wouldn't throw her away
for something like that.
Well let's see what it can do!
I wonder how you turn it on.
Shinbo said that they start up
when you push the switch.
Switch... Switch... Switch...
Switch... Switch...
Where's it at?
Oh man.
I can't find that darn switch.
I've already tried pushing
every place I can think of.
I pushed here, and there.
And this, and even these!
Even those.
I've pushed every inch of
this computer I can find!
Everywhere! Except...
It can't be...
No. Not there?!
Impossible!
How can that possibly
be the switch!
But that's really the only
place I haven't tried yet.
I'm not doing this
because I'm
perverted or anything.
But what's the point of having
it if it doesn't work?!
Yeah! That's right.
Right.
Chi?
Wha?! Uh... Chi? Eh... Huh?
Chi? What's that?
Oh! I get it. Is that your name?
Chi!!
Wait a minute!
What's going on here?!
The Persocom has started moving,
but it only says "Chi".
And it's naked, and on top
of that it's really cute.
Chi?
I know!
I've heard of something
like this happening before.
A beautiful girl barges into
your life outta nowhere,
who happens to
have special powers,
and can do almost anything!
Suddenly she falls in love
with the guy she lives with,
and she'll do all
sorts of things for him!
Cooking, cleaning,
even THOSE kinda things!
Chi?
Thank you! I am SO lucky!
Y-Yeah!
It's me, Shinbo,
I'm just goin' out to
the public bathhouse.
I was wondering if you
wanted to come along.
This apartment doesn't
have any bathtubs.
Okay, that sounds good!
Are you ready to go now?
I'll be right there.
Uh, naked!
Of course, what's the
big deal? It's a bath.
Don't tell me you're
the type that has
to wear a bathing suit
in a public bath.
Chi...
No of course not. No problem!
Oh no what am I gonna
do? This is not good!
Shhh.
Okay clothes, clothes,
where are the clothes?
I've got to find
something for her to wear!
Oh man!
I should have
labeled these boxes
so I'd know what's inside!
Yes! A towel!
This'll work for now.
Chi...
That looks even more suspicious.
Hey, are you ready or not?!
There has got to be
something for her to wear!
Come on!
Unh...
No not that!!
What's wrong?
Can't you find your
stuff for the bath?
No! That's not it...
You want some help?
No, I'm fine!!
Don't be so embarrassed.
Hey, the door's unlocked.
Ah!!! I forgot
to lock the door!!
I've got to hide
her somewhere! Nice!
What's the matter?
Hey, what happened?
Your room is trashed!
Hey, relax man.
The bath's open
till midnight, ya know.
What's wrong?
Your nose is bleeding!
I'm fine, really.
It's no big deal. I just fell!
Okay, but I don't
know how you're gonna
find your shampoo or anything.
I guess you can use mine.
Uh, thanks.
You need a towel?
Got one right here.
But I mean I was already kinda,
uh, using it for something.
For what?
Um! Nothing to worry about.
It doesn't concern you at all!
Yeah, whatever.
I'll be waiting in my room, so
come by when you're ready.
Great! No problem!
I'll be there in a sec!
See ya.
Chi?
Hey...
Yeah?
Now what're you doing?
Oh nothing I guess
I just tripped again.
Is something wrong with you?
Chi?
No! No, nothing at all!
Well look, if you can't find
a change of clothes,
you can borrow some of mine.
Chi?
That's all right.
I can find some
of my own clothes!
I'll be over there in a second
so just wait for
me in your room.
Okay? Okay?
Yeah. Okay.
Oh by the way...
What?!
Chill out!
Don't surprise me like that!
Sorry dude.
What'd you wanna say?
Oh, yeah.
The bath costs 400 yen.
If you wanna use the sauna
and stuff, it's an extra 300.
Do you have enough?
Yeah. Fine. Thanks.
Chi.
I'm so tired.
Huh?!
You stay right here. Okay? Okay?
Chi.
What now, Shinbo? Cut it out.
Huh?!! M-Miss Hibiya!
Um, hi! So what
can I do for you?
I'm afraid I made
too much kinpira.
If you don't dislike
this kind of food.
Wow, that looks great!
Is that for me?!
Yes.
Ah! Thank you so much!
Oh, it's no problem
since I made too
much for just me.
I hope you don't mind.
Why would I mind?
I'm thrilled! This is great!
It's totally fine with me!
Oh, I'm so glad.
Well, if I make anything
else I think is good,
I'll be sure to
bring it up for you.
Wow! You will?!
Sure! If you're happy
with my cooking.
Yeah! I'll be happy alright!
Thank you very much!
Chi.
You're really too nice.
I'm touched!
Chi.
You're the best!
Oh!
Huh? Waaahhh!!
Chi?
My oh my.
No really, it's not
what you think!
It's a Persocom!
My! What a cute little Persocom!
Yeah, well, it's a
Persocom all right.
Well Mr. Motosuwa
and Miss Persocom.
Have a very good night.
Chi.
Wow. What a cool manager.
I bet she thinks I'm
a pervert or something.
She probably thinks
I'm stripping my
Persocom just for fun.
Mmm, this is good.
What?
Now you're not
gonna come with me?
Why not?
Hey, sorry man.
I just feel like I should finish
cleaning up my
place, that's all.
Well, alright then,
what can I say?
I'm so sorry!
It's fine. Chill out.
Don't worry about it.
Chi.
Very nice!
Why am I sweating so much?
I'm just dealing
with a Persocom here!
I know I need to
calm down. That's it.
I'll just calm down, calm down!
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
Chi.
Hey.
Chi?
Is "Chi" the only
thing you can say?
Chi.
Well, I guess this
was a Persocom
that I found out in the garbage.
Hmm, I wonder if it's broken
or messed up or something.
Hey, don't look so sad.
Are you afraid
that you're gonna be
thrown away again?
C'mon, I'm the
one who rescued you!
I'll take good care of you!
Chi!
She really is cute, though.
So soft. So warm.
If she didn't have those ears,
she'd be just
like a normal girl.
And her breasts are so soft too!
How lucky am I to find
such a cute Persocom?
Yes!
Chi, Chi!
But all she ever says is "Chi."
I wonder if she's
broken or something.
I really don't know
anything about these things.
Chi.
But don't worry!
I'm gonna find out
what's wrong with her
when I talk to this guy
that Shinbo introduces me to.
Apparently he's knows
everything about Persocoms!
Chi!
The next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Goes Out." Huh?
An urban legend
circulating the 'net?