Hideki.
Here he is.
Oh, sorry!
He looks desperate.
Well, he's definitely very
worried about Miss Chi.
Motosuwa is a good guy.
Successful dismount!
Sumomo avoids
falling on her face!
Here.
Do you feel better?
Yeah. Thanks, Minoru. I'm sorry.
So is that all
you have to go on?
Well, I know for a fact
that she was at the bookstore,
but that's about it.
She might have been in an
accident; for all I know.
Or perhaps was
abducted by someone.
Abducted?!
It's a possibility.
It could always be someone
related to that image, you know.
Excuse me;
I'm sorry to interrupt.
What is it?
I don't suppose you mind
if I make a suggestion?
There's another line of
inquiry you should explore.
If you think you
might know something,
just go ahead and tell us.
Although it is
possible that the one
who e-mailed the
image is also somehow
involved in Chi's disappearance,
we don't know this.
In fact, any number
of people could have
found out about Miss Chi by now.
Lord Minoru,
you posted a message
about Chi on a Persocom
website a while ago.
Do you think that might
have something to do with it?
Perhaps someone who
saw that post happened
to notice Miss Chi in town,
and then proceeded to--
...steal her for their
own personal interests.
You mean...?
Mr. Motosuwa?
Whatever it is, all I can
do now is keep looking.
So, if you hear anything,
please call Sumomo.
Ueda!
Huh? Motosuwa.
Well, from the looks of it,
I guess you still
haven't found her.
No.
After I closed the
shop for the day,
I decided to take a look
around the area myself.
I thought it would
be a good idea
to see if any of the other
shop owners knew anything.
Sorry to bother you.
No, I really should
have gotten in touch
with you much earlier
about something like this.
Come on; I'll help
you look for her.
But, you don't...
Think about it:
it'll be a lot faster if
we look together. Right?
Yeah. Thank you very much.
Sure, I've already
tried all the places
on the other
side of the florist.
Right
Well, good luck.
Sorry I wasn't able
help to you out any.
Thanks a lot anyway.
Thank you very much.
A longhaired Persocom?
No, I haven't seen one.
I see. Well,
thanks for your time.
This girl?
No, I don't think
I've seen her around.
Have you asked at any
of the other shops yet?
Well, not all of them, just
the ones on the other side.
I see.
Well, if you're gonna go
to all the shops in the strip,
wouldn't it be faster
to use a Persocom,
and have it post a message
about her on the bulletin board?
Maybe Tirol's Persocom-
Oh, that's right: you don't have
a Persocom at the moment,
do you, Mr. Ueda?
No.
All right.
I'd be happy to post
something for you if you like.
I'll contact you if
I find out anything.
Can you contact her instead?
Sumomo is ready to
transfer her data!
Connect me to your Persocom,
and I'll give you my
contact information!
Sure, no problem.
Anything would help, so even
if it isn't much, please call.
All right, then.
Hey Motosuwa, you all right?
Yeah.
Of course this is
just one possibility,
and I know it may not be true,
but, from what I heard earlier,
it looks like Chi could have
been abducted by someone.
And if she was,
she could be suffering,
or in a very tough
spot right now.
And when I start to
think about that, I...
Okay, I'm gonna take a look
around here one more time!
Telephone!
Answer it!
Aye!
Yo, Motosuwa!
Shinbo!
Hey, listen, I finally
got the okay from Takako.
So I thought I'd at
least let you know--
I'm sorry, but...
You picked a really
bad time to call.
Huh?
I see.
Look, Shinbo, do Persocoms
feel pain like people do?
Does it hurt if someone does
something horrible to them?
Motosuwa...
You know,
Persocoms aren't like that.
Unless they're
programmed for it, I guess.
But even if a Persocom is
programmed with a sense of pain,
all you have to do to
get rid of it is erase
those memories from the hard
drive and the memory slots.
Erase?
Yeah.
If you delete the data,
the Persocom loses it forever.
Physical pain and emotional
pain... everything.
Even though they
look like humans...
Persocoms are just
Persocoms after all.
Anyway, I'll let you
know if I hear anything.
Try not to let it
get to ya. See ya.
I'm... still worried.
But it doesn't matter
if I'm worried or not.
What about Chi? Where is she?
Mr. Motosuwa, do you
think you could hang out
with me for a little while?
I know what
Shinbo's talking about.
It's just that
I don't know what to do.
And besides,
I'm sure that Chi had
at least one previous owner.
And, since Chi is a Persocom,
it's no big surprise
that her memory's gone.
But when I look at Chi,
I just can't think
of her like that.
I'm sorry, I know I'm
not making any sense.
No, I understand.
I do, because I was confused
about the exact same thing once.
To tell you the truth,
I don't talk about it much,
but for a while,
I was married to a Persocom.
It's that store
right over there.
That store?
It was right after
I opened Tirol.
I'll never forget
the day I met her.
The guy at the store suggested
that I buy one of
the newest models.
And they were all pretty,
but I couldn't really
tell them apart.
And then... There she was.
Back there in the corner,
marked down with
a bargain price tag,
under a thin layer of dust.
When I asked about her,
he said that she
was an old model
that was about to
go out of production.
And then, the next thing I knew
I'd already bought her
and we were home.
I tried to make some
sense out of the manual,
and somehow got her to boot up.
And then she said-
Nice to meet you.
And what would your name be?
Huh?
I'm Ueda. Hiroyasu Ueda.
Mr. Ueda. I have
input your name.
Does this mean that
you're my master, Mr. Ueda?
What? Well, I guess it does.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I guess you could say it
was love at first sight.
She was always smiling
and full of energy.
If something bad happened to me,
she cheered me up,
and when things went well
she was happy for me.
She was by my side
no matter what happened.
Before I knew it, I'd completely
fallen in love with her.
Her, a Persocom.
So...
So, I actually went
through with it.
I proposed to her.
She nodded yes, with
her usual happy smile.
Yeah, but, can you
really marry a Persocom?
Well, no, it's not possible
from a legal point of view.
But it was definitely
a real marriage.
Besides, you can give
property to Persocoms,
and they can also
inherit your belongings.
But your family.
Didn't your folks care or
try to talk you out of it?
No, both of them had
passed away by then.
The ceremony was
just beautiful. Perfect.
We had a wedding dress made,
and held the service
in a small restaurant.
Someone even wrote
an article about it,
and the people in the
shopping strip teased me
a lot and made fun of me.
But, I was happy...
that I could be
together with her,
and that she would
continue to smile like that.
And yet, by then,
the signs had already
started to appear.
The signs?
She started to forget things.
Little by little,
all sorts of things.
At the time,
I thought it was just me,
so I wasn't all that concerned.
But then she started to forget
things from the day before,
and little errors about where
we kept certain
things in the shop.
It started getting
worse and worse.
And then she would
forget what kind of cake
a customer had ordered
just seconds before.
I looked through
all sorts of books,
but I couldn't figure
it out what it was.
So I took her back to
the electronics store.
The hard drive
is completely shot.
You're gonna have to
replace the whole thing
if you want to fix it.
But she'll get better
if I replace it, right?
Yeah.
But since it's an older model,
there's no way I can guarantee
that the data's gonna
transfer over properly.
What?
When we re-boot, it
might lose everything.
Yes, but she'd lose
her memory then.
Is that what you're telling me?
But that's just too cruel!
You don't have to worry so much.
The Persocom won't feel any
sadness or pain whatsoever.
Because she'll have
completely forgotten
everything she learned.
I just couldn't
handle her losing
everything I'd shared with her.
The thought was
just unbearable to me.
I took her to some
other shops to see
if anyone could help her,
but it was always the same.
So after that,
I decided to bring her
home without doing anything.
Nice to meet you.
And what would your name be?
I'm Ueda. Hiroyasu Ueda.
Mr. Ueda. I have
input your name.
Does this mean that
you're my master, Mr. Ueda?
The situation was bad enough,
but her condition
got even worse.
She started to forget things
that had happened just
a few seconds before.
Nice to meet you.
And what would your name be?
And what would your name be...?
But even then,
I still couldn't send
her out to be repaired.
Even if it was
only a little bit,
or even just once in a while...
The fact that she
could still remember me
with that broken hard
drive was something
I just couldn't bring
myself to let go of.
But then, one rainy day
after she'd been
like that for a while,
we went out shopping together.
By that time, it was
very hard for her
to live even a
simple everyday life.
I never knew what she might do
if I took my eyes off of her.
I thought about her constantly,
and I couldn't sleep,
there was nothing I could do.
I guess I was in a daze.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sure she was in such a state
that she didn't understand
the consequences
of being hit by a truck.
But, I somehow felt
that she'd sacrificed
her own life to save me.
Pretty strange, huh?
She was still able to
do an incredible thing
like that when she
could barely even function.
No, it's not strange!
Not in the least.
I think she saved
your life even though
she knew what would happen.
Thanks for saying that.
Immediately after the accident,
I took her to the shop
where I bought her.
But they said that
she was so torn up
that they could
never re-boot her.
Her body was shattered.
They said if I wanted,
they'd try to find another
one of the same model.
A different one
that looked the same.
But, to me, there could
never be another "her."
She was a Persocom,
and not a living creature,
but for me, she had
died there in the rain.
I knew that there
was nothing to repair;
she couldn't feel or
remember anything anymore.
But...
I still remember her.
I remember everything about her.
Her face, her voice,
her movements...
The good times
and the bad times.
I'm pretty sure I'll
never forget any of that.
That's just how
you feel, isn't it?
Even if Chi doesn't remember
what the two of you have shared,
you'll always remember,
won't you, Motosuwa?
If something happened to Chi,
you'd still remember
her, wouldn't you?
Yes.
So it wouldn't have been
all for nothing, then.
Even if they were
able to erase it
from the hard drive somehow,
not as long as you
still remember, Motosuwa.
That's why you need to find Chi.
Yes.
Even though I don't have
an idea where she could be,
I'm gonna look for her.
I'm sure she'll
be waiting for you.
Yeah.
Motosuwa!
That might be who took Chi!
What's going on?
Chi.
Hey you!
Yumi?
Miss Ohmura.
Huh?
Yumi!
You might as well
save your breath.
Huh?
I'm afraid she's not gonna
come back as long as I'm here.
Well, as you can see,
she gets really sad
whenever I'm around her.
Do you know
something about Yumi?
For the moment,
the most important thing
for us to do is to find Chi.
What's this file?
It's an access log from
the custom-made Persocom
website where
I posted that message
about Chi a while back.
I had it sent to me.
I'm surprised that the
webmaster would do this.
They owe me, so I cashed
in the favor this time.
With a list, I can check
them off one by one
and see if any of
them match the person
who sent that image.
The reason Miss Chi
disappeared like this might be
because I didn't think through
before I posted on that site.
Sorry to cause you such trouble.
It's all because I had
to open my big mouth.
Thank you.
What?
If you hadn't brought it up,
it never would have even
occurred to me, Yuzuki.
It was a very good suggestion.
Lord Minoru.
I'm very happy that
you brought it up.
Thank you, Lord Minoru.
I just thought that your sister
would have done the same thing,
so that's why
I mentioned it to you.
Well you're right.
My sister truly was very kind,
and would gently point out
my mistakes and oversights.
Oh, I see.
But, I wasn't happy just
because you did something that
my sister would have done.
New mail has arrived. This is...
What's wrong?
The return address matches
the one that sent
the image of Miss Chi!
Yumi and Mr. Ueda, they
know each other somehow,
but for some reason,
Yumi never even mentioned it.
I can't think about that now,
I have to look for Chi!
Let's go, Sumomo!
Aye!
I begin my search again today
for the one who is only for me.
The person who will love me
because I am who I am.
The person who
will still love me
even if I cannot
grant his dreams.
The special one for Chi.
Next episode, Chobits:
"Chi Wants."
The one for Chi
and only for Chi.