I just don't get it at all.
Unh! What's the matter with me?!
This'll take forever;
I'll never make it!
Huh?
Senpai!
Yumi?
Uh, Yumi.
What's this all about?
Senpai.
Gah!
M-Miss Manager!
What on earth
are you doing here?
Huh?
Ahh.
But, what the heck has
suddenly come over all of you?
Ooh.
Mmm.
Do me.
Do?
W-What on earth's going on?
Are you the one who is
for me, and only for me?
Or are you not the
one who is for me.
Which is it?
Tell me.
Which?
Hideki...
Hideki.
Huh?
You were saying uhh, uhh,
and going round and round.
Is Hideki alright?
Round and round?
I guess I was moaning
from that nightmare.
That nightmare?
Well, it's... Hmm.
Well, it means to
have a scary dream,
and thrash around, like
I must've been doing just now.
Hideki was scared?
Huh? Oh, don't worry; I'm fine.
I said it was scary,
but it's just a dream.
Dream?
Chi doesn't understand
about "dream."
Oh, I guess you probably
wouldn't have dreams,
because you're a Persocom.
But it's no big deal.
Dreams aren't actually
real, after all.
See? I'm full of energy!
Energy?
Huh?
Full of energy here, too?
Gah!
Chi.
Geez, what a great morning
this turned out to be.
And that was such
a strange dream, too.
Do me, Hideki.
That was so nice.
Can't think about that right now
Let's see, anything else?
Wallet, right. Gotta have that.
What is Hideki doing?
No matter how many times I look,
there's never any money inside.
Money?
Is that a good thing to have?
Of course it is.
Hey, you can get just
about anything you want
if you've got enough money.
Study books, clothing,
food, whatever you need.
But there's only
so much you can do,
and right now I couldn't
take on another job
even if I wanted to.
Another job?
Yeah, it means to work.
When you go out and do that,
they give you money.
I pretty much have
to buy the study guides.
I guess I'll just cut
back to one meal a day.
As for the porno mags...
Hmmm.
I guess I can borrow
them from my boss.
Chi will get a job.
Huh?
Can Chi do this job?
"Would you like to
make 2 million a month?"
"Dominatrix wanted."
No way!
Ch-
Chi can't get job?
Huh?
Uh, no, no it's not like that.
Hey, I didn't mean you can't
get a job if you want to,
it's-yeah, it's just
the problem is:
what kind of job,
that's all I meant.
So then, Chi can get a job.
Huh?
Hmm.
Well, if it's a good job.
Yes, Chi will do a good job!
What's the use?
But any shady jobs are
completely off limits.
We can talk about
it when I get back.
Okay, well I have to go now.
Take care of yourself.
Good, good; shady, bad.
Shady jobs bad;
good jobs, good. Chi learned.
Chi gets good job.
Hideki is happy.
Work, prep school,
work, prep school...
It's the same ol' thing,
day in and day out.
This starving student
thing is tough.
Chi really wants a job, huh?
No, it's impossible, isn't it?
What's impossible?
Ahh! Oh,Yumi.
Huh? Not working today?
Nope, I'm going to
go shopping right now.
Can I give you a hand
carrying that, Senpai?
Ahh.
Yumi!
Gah!
What's wrong?
Well, it's heavy.
Oh, is it?
By the way,
Senpai, what was that
you were saying about a job?
Huh?! How'd you
know about that?!
Because I overheard you saying
something about it just now.
I was just doing it again.
You're not going
to quit, are you?
Huh?
You're not saying
you've found another job,
and you're going to
be leaving us, are you?
Oh no, I didn't mean that,
I didn't say that at all!
I'm not going to quit.
I couldn't; if I quit my job,
I wouldn't be able to survive!
I'm so glad!
"I'm so glad!"
"I'm so glad!" "I'm so glad!"
Ohh! Yumi's smile... It's so-
Wait a minute,
that look on her face...
That's definitely one
of those looks like
she's really worried
I might quit my job.
Wait a sec. Could it be?
Could it be?
Then what were you
so worked up about?
Oh, it was about Chi.
Chi?
Yeah.
Oh, that's right; that was your
Persocom's name, wasn't it?
Yeah she suddenly started
talking about getting a job.
I'm a little bit
worried about it.
Persocom.
I'm sure your Persocom
is a very cute one, too.
Huh?
Yumi? Ugh!
What's the matter with me?!
I'm even more of
a geek than usual.
What is it, Senpai?
Are you hungry?
No, things are just
a little tight this month,
I had to cut back on food.
I mean, hey, it's nothing!
Well, gotta go get
ready to open up!
Get good job... None.
Hey, there!
Whatcha doin'?
Huh?
Hey, wait, it's a Persocom.
But I gotta say she's
an awfully cute one.
So, who's your owner?
Why ya out alone?
My owner is called Hideki.
Chi, looking for a job.
A job?
Oh, hey what a coincidence...
I know one: it's a
really good job too;
really short hours,
and great pay.
A good job?
Oh yeah, a really good job!
I'll tell ya all
about it, come on.
It's a little ways away
from here, but don't worry.
I'll take you over to the place.
You'll like it.
The work's really easy.
I have an order
for two lemon sours!
My Pleasure!
But I can't stop now; I gotta
get these finished first.
Are these glasses
ready for me to take now?
Uh, sure.
Good, then, please excuse me.
Boy, these new
Persocoms really are
something when
you think about it.
They notice things,
and they seem
to be able to do
just about anything.
But.
I don't think it'd be
quite the same way with Chi.
Senpai.
Hey Yumi, what's up?
It's just about the end
of your shift, isn't it?
Would you like
to have some dinner
with me before you go?
Huh? Me?
It sounded like you might
be a little bit hungry today,
so I just happened to buy a
little more food than I needed.
It's not very good for your body
to cut back on food, you know.
And anyway, you can't study
if you don't have energy.
So I'm gonna have dinner now,
and if you don't
have any objection...
Yumi's homemade dinner.
Okay, say "aah!"
Aah!
Oh, but...
Actually, if you've got a
Persocom back at your apartment,
it's probably busy making dinner
for you right now, isn't it?
No.
It's not like there are
that many things
Chi can do right yet.
That's why I was concerned
about her getting a job.
I was afraid she might wind up
in a dangerous situation
or something like that.
Are you really
worried about her?
Oh yeah, more than just worried.
Hey, I'm not even really sure
exactly what she can do.
Oh, she'll be alright.
A Persocom can do
pretty much anything,
and just about any job.
Uh , Yumi?
So, you are going
to eat dinner, aren't you?
Oh, sure.
Great, well I'll
be up in the office.
Yumi always seems
to get so depressed
whenever we talk
about Persocoms.
Did she have a bad experience
with one or something?
Hmm.
I should watch what
I say around her.
Now, try talking.
Yes.
The Kanto area tomorrow
will be partially cloudy,
and in some areas,
low-lying fog may develop.
That's fine.
Conversation good.
Now, I just need
to check the CPU-
Is something wrong?
It's something about Chi.
I did a search for this
on the net a while back.
Apparently I got a hit.
Yuzuki, switch over.
Right.
Huh?
What ?
What's going on?
You are a cute one, aren't you?
Okay, now don't
let it bother you any,
nobody can hear
me except for you.
I'm gonna start streaming
the feed onto the web now,
and depending on
how many hits you get,
you might even make
more than we said.
So knock 'em dead.
Chi?
Well, I thought
I'd seen them all,
and I gotta say I've checked out
a bunch of Persocoms in my day,
but I've never seen anyone
nearly as cute as this one.
Hey, what brand are you?
Brand?
Hmm. It must be custom-made.
Alright, so who made you, then?
Chi has no idea
what person made Chi.
Huh? Your owner,
this Hideki guy?
He wasn't the one who made you?
Hideki found Chi.
But Hideki didn't make Chi.
He found you?!
Huh?
So this Hideki somehow managed
to get a Persocom
like you for free?
Talk about lucky.
Lucky?
I mean, he should be happy.
Should be happy.
Happy. Is that good for Hideki?
Oh yeah, people are better
off when they're happy.
Happy.
Hideki's happy.
Happy to find Chi.
The physical appearance
matches perfectly.
There's no room for doubt.
It's definitely Chi
But I'm quite sure
Mr. Motosuwa would
never make Chi work
in a place like this one.
Yuzuki, send
Mr. Shinbo an e-mail.
Right.
You have mail! You have mail!
Huh?
Mail? Who's it from?
From Mr. Minoru Kokubunji,
and it's marked "urgent"!
Urgent? Read it, would ya?
Aye!
I didn't mean to spring
it on you so suddenly,
it's just that my whole family
seems to be eating out today.
And I don't know about you,
but I don't like eating alone.
I'm really glad you
could stay, Senpai.
"I'm really glad you
could stay, Senpai."
"I'm really glad, Senpai."
I'm such a lucky guy!
I'll make dinner right away,
so it'll be just a minute, okay?
Oh, don't worry
about me, I'm fine.
You don't have to hurry.
Wow, you're pretty
good with that thing.
I guess you do a
lotta cooking, huh?
Well, I wouldn't say that.
I do bake a lot of
sweets, though, but...
I don't know how good a
cook I am for regular food,
so if it's bad, you don't
have to finish it or anything.
Oh, that's all right.
If it's something you make,
Yumi, I'm sure I'll eat it all.
Uh-oh, now you've done it!
That was a promise!
Wah-hooo!
Ooops!
Hey, what's the matter?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just dropped the lid for
the salt shaker, that's all.
Oh I see.
Do you need any help?
Sure, how about
giving this a taste?
So, what do you think?
Delicious!
You're a great cook, Yumi!
You really think so?
That's great!
Senpai, so tell me,
how do you like your eggs?
Do you prefer them sweet or not?
Hmm. Not too sweet.
My pleasure!
Hey, this is sorta fun,
don'tcha think?
It's almost like
we're newlyweds.
Gah?!
Oh, but if we were married,
that would make me a little
too young, wouldn't it?
No, hey, that's not true at all!
In fact, I really like
the Young Wife series!
Wife series?
Argh.
Uh, I...
How could I have said that?
Motosuwa!
There's someone here to see you!
Shinbo?
What's the matter, Shinbo?
I've never seen you
so worked up.
Okay, well it's like this:
are you making
your Persocom work or something?
Huh? Not really.
That's what I thought.
I just got an
e-mail from Kokubunji.
Sumomo!
Aye!Replaying message!
Chi is in a peep show.
They're also doing
streaming video,
and it's called: "Kitty-cat's
live hot girls meow meow."
In a... peep... show?
You mean a peep show?
How'd that happen?!
Chi doesn't understand
much about the world,
and she doesn't
have any common sense!
If something
happened to her, I'd-
That's-That's why I tried
to teach her about things!
What have I done?
Money?
Is that a good thing to have?
Impossible!
You gotta tell me
where this place is.
Tell me right now!
Hey calm down, willya?
Sumomo's already got the address
of the place, so don't worry.
She can help you find it.
Where is it?!
Waah!
Master, he's scary!
Ugh.
Come on, we're counting on you.
Aye. Then I will start
my navigation mode now.
Now proceed straight this way.
And turn left, turn left!
You have strayed
from the guide route!
Alrighty then.
It's just about show time.
You about ready in there?
Then, let's get to it.
What is Chi supposed to do?
Well, you should strip
your clothes off bit by bit.
Chi strip?
Make sure you give a
good show for the customers,
lots of sexy poses like this,
you know what I mean?
The customers?
Yeah. See all the holes
in the wall around you?
They're lookin' in
from there, get it?
Hey, what are you doin'?
Gyah!
Hey, don't do that!
Get back in your chair!
Chi?
Continue straight ahead!
Turn right at the next alley!
Okay, now let's try
the top, alright?
That's good, lower it slowly.
Right, now it's
time for your bra.
Hey whatcha doin'?
Don't tell me you don't
know how to take off your bra!
Chi never had a bra before.
She's never put on a bra?
That Hideki must be
some kinda puritan.
Oh, alright.
That's fine;
go for the underpants.
Underpants. Underpants.
Underpants.
Okay, that'll do.
You can drop them now.
Okay, what say we spice things
up a little with the fingers?
Fingers?
Yeah, put your fingers in.
Chi?
No no no!
Not in there, not in there!
Fingers in where?
In between your legs.
Chi.
Stop.
Is something wrong?
Stop?
Don't touch there.
Don't.
Touch.
There.
Take the next left turn here!
You idiot!
Sorry 'bout that!
Chi!
Hey, what's the
matter? Hey? Hello!
Well that's about it.
Remember this well.
You rebooted by pushing the
switch deep inside there.
And so, regardless
of what happens,
until the day someone
who truly loves you appears,
never let anyone touch you here.
Nobody.
That's right.
Don't let anyone
touch you. Anyone.
The building is
300 meters ahead.
Your destination
is the 7th floor!
There it is!
Come on, what's the
matter all of a sudden?
Didn't you understand
what I said?
It's simple, you know?
Let's give it a try.
Stop.
Are you running some
kinda special program,
is that what it means?
Come on, Hideki.
I guess I have to...
Here.
Like this.
W-What's that?
Chi!
Ta-dah!
Now, which of the
following is a shady job?
Chi chi chi chi chi...
Convenience store clerk,
leaflet passer-outer,
dishwasher, manga drawing
assistant, traffic consultant,
waitress, paperboy, anime
producer, construction worker,
tutor, phone operator,
bartender, roadie, movie extra,
model, peep show stripper.
And the answer is:
it would have to be the
peep show stripper, right?
So, how in the world did you end
up there? Chi!
The next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Bewildered."
Chi found a good job
just like Hideki said.