The building is
300 meters ahead.
Your destination
is the 7th floor!
There it is!
W-What's that?
Chi!
Where's Chi?!
What did you do to her?
Hey! Darn it!
So, where the heck did she go?
Hey, look up there!
Do you see her?
Hey, look at that!
Chi! Where'd you go, Chi?!
Answer me!
Where did she go?
Huh?
Now how on earth could
a thing like that happen?
Yuzuki, replay at
1/4 speed for me!
Right.
Yuzuki!
Darn it. Where is she?
Sumomo, we've gotta get
a hold of Minoru right now!
Can you try calling him at home?
Huh? Hey, Sumomo.
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Sumomo! Sumomo!
No way, she can't be broken!
Say something, Sumomo!
Darn it.
And just when
I borrowed her, too.
Now what have I done?
This is the
north entrance police.
Huh?
All of you who've
stopped your Persocoms
in the courtyard in
front of the train station,
please move them immediately!
Once again,
your attention please.
This is the police
office located
inside the north entrance
of the train station.
All of you who've
stopped your Persocoms
in the courtyard in
front of the train station,
please move them immediately!
You are impeding
the flow of traffic.
Please get them
cleared away immediately.
Hey, what's going on?
Is ours working?
Naw, it's down.
Can't seem to
figure it out, either.
That isn't what
I wanted to hear.
This computer
isn't any good either.
It won't reboot.
I'd like to know just
what the hell's going on.
What's up? Did something happen?
So it's not moving
at all then, is it?
Uh, no.
I don't suppose you have any
idea how all of this happened?
Well just before,
when it was looking up
at the Persocom standing
on top of the clock,
it suddenly stopped moving.
Clock? Persocom?
Hmm? Well there isn't
anything like that around here.
Uh, yeah...
Chi, where are you?!
Come on, where are you? Chi!
Chi!
Chi, can you hear me?!
Hideki?
What is it? Is there
something the matter?
Actually, that's
what I'd like to know.
Oh, that was scary!
What was scary?
Chi has been located!
I repeat: Chi has been located!
Sumomo.
Chi.
Alright, I've gotta find
some way to get her home.
1, 2, 3.
I guess that's it then.
There's no other way.
Hey mister, is that a Persocom?
Yeah.
Looks like it froze
while you guys were out.
I suppose Persocoms
are rather useful,
but it looks like it cost you
this time, didn't it, Buddy?
I guess. Yeah
But, Chi is a very
valuable Persocom for me.
And so...
I don't know how,
but that didn't
feel like a dream.
It felt like I was in
some kind of action movie.
That whole thing is
one big mystery to me.
And it all really happened, too.
Yet here she is,
sleeping so peacefully.
But, wait...
She looks like she's sleeping,
but that's not
really sleeping. Is it?
Come to think of it, she
hasn't moved a bit all night.
It's not like she'll
never move again, right?
Chi.
What would happen
if she never moved again?
Chi! Wake up, okay? Chi!
What if... she stayed
like this forever?
Chi! What's wrong with you, Chi?
Wake up!
Chi.
Hideki.
Chi!
Hideki! Hideki! Hideki!
Hey!
Chi.
I'm glad, Chi.
Lord Minoru,
Would you like some more tea?
Thanks, I could
certainly use some.
Miss Chi, I wonder
if she is alright now.
Mr. Shinbo sent me an
e-mail a little while ago.
They managed to
find her somehow,
and were able to bring her home.
Oh how fortunate.
I'm so glad it all worked out.
What I don't understand...
is what could make
every computer
in the area freeze up like
that all of a sudden.
And, you don't
seem to understand
why it happened either.
Isn't that right, Yuzuki?
I do not.
However...
However?
Surely...
I think...
Yes, I'm sure I heard some
kind of voice in my head.
Who was it?
I don't know.
Although...
That's right...
It seems to me that
it was very familiar,
as if the voice
of someone I know.
It seemed.
It was a job.
Oh yeah? I don't suppose
you'd care to repeat that?
Chi got a job yesterday.
I told you no, what's so
difficult to understand?
I said no working at
anything shady like that!
Hideki said no,
don't do a shady job.
So, Chi didn't do a shady job.
Well as far as jobs go,
I'd have to say a peep
show is pretty shady.
Chi?
But the man told Chi,
"Oh yeah, it's a
really good job."
Oh! Those kinda guys'll
always say things like that!
He said Hideki would be
happy if Chi finds good job.
Huh?
And Hideki said that he wanted
to buy lots of
things with money.
Yeah, you're right. I did.
I guess I must've
said some stupid things
that made you do that.
Ah...
Huh?
Did Chi make mistake?
Um.
Is Chi bad?
Well, no. Not bad.
Chi isn't bad or anything.
I didn't mean...
You're not bad at all.
Is that true?
Yeah!
Oh, Chi.
Don't think that, Chi.
You're not bad!
Chi does not want
Hideki to hate Chi.
Because Hideki is Chi's-
I really appreciate
what you're saying, but...
Um... look, Chi, I don't
want you to think you have
to go out of your way
to work or anything.
But why?
Hideki told Chi that
would make him happy.
Mmm...
Okay, what do you
think about this?
If you really want to get a job,
I'll go help you find one.
But until I find you something,
you'll have to stay
at home. How 'bout that?
Thank you, Hideki.
Chi's happy now.
No, not you.
After all, I'm the one
who should be saying thanks.
I really mean it.
Thank you, Chi.
'Cause you did it all for me.
Chi.
You need to be careful here,
due to the fact that this
particular phrase uses "tamae."
A part-time job...
one that isn't shady
or even questionable,
But that'll still
consider hiring Chi,
even though she's a little short
in the common sense department.
Hmm...
I wonder if it's even possible
to find a place that perfect.
Please don't be
worried about last night.
I didn't take
offense or anything.
Yeah, well that's good,
but I was really looking forward
to your home-cooked meal, Yumi.
Anyway, as it turned out,
it was a good thing your
Persocom was all right.
Yeah, that's true.
But she still doesn't
understand what she did.
And I think she
just might be liable
to do something strange again,
if I don't manage
to find her a new job.
Oh I see.
I bet that won't very easy.
Well, actually,
it was pretty tough,
but I finally found one.
Huh?
A job for my Persocom.
It's a bakery right
here in the mall.
I'm sure you must've
seen it at some point.
It's a place called Tirol.
And as luck would have it,
they're having some kind
of festival at the moment,
which sounded like
just the thing to me.
Anniversary...
Huh?
It's their 5th anniversary
festival, right?
It says it right here.
That's what the
flyer's all about.
Yeah, that's right!
So I talked to the owner
about it, he was very nice,
and he said he'd
be happy to hire Chi!
Man, I'm so relieved.
I was thinking I'd never
be able to find something.
That's so great.
You sure are lucky!
Okay, everybody,
time to open up.
My Pleasure!
Ready, Yumi?
Sure!
Come on in.
Everyone's welcome to Tirol
Bakery's fifth anniversary fair.
Treat yourself
and join us inside.
Free gifts and prizes for
everyone who buys pastries.
Come on in.
Everyone's welcome to Tirol
Bakery's fifth anniversary fair.
We have gifts and
prizes for everyone...
Look at her! Isn't she cute?
Yeah, she is, isn't she?
Is that really a Persocom?
Yeah, of course.
Take a look at the ears.
It's a dead give-away.
Oh wow, well,
she's still really cute!
So, is that a
Persocom out there?
Yep.
Wow, she's pretty cute, huh?
In the "saburai" used
in this example taken
from the Ise Stories, and the
"saburai" used in the example
taken from Taketori Stories,
we should note
that the following
words "te" and "ken"--
I wonder if she's
getting along okay,
and not causing
too much trouble.
Chi!
Thanks for all the hard work.
Chi.
It's almost closing
time, so finish up.
And thank you
very much for today.
Finish up?
Yes, Chi.
To "finish up" means your
job is done for the day,
and you can go home
Chi doesn't understand
what you say,
because this is first job.
Chi didn't make the
mistake, did she?
You didn't make any
mistakes at all, Chi.
In fact, your work
today was impeccable,
and I really appreciate
all the effort.
So Chi can get
money and go home?
Of course you can.
Here you go. This is for you.
Inside is your pay
for today's work.
Is this money?
No, that's only an envelope.
You'll find the money
inside when you open it up.
Can Chi buy something now...
with money inside?
Of course, that's what it's for!
Chis is now able to
buy things Hideki wants
with money inside envelope.
Chi has lots of things
not understood about.
So, must learn all about them.
Manager, Hiroyasu Ueda!
Please teach Chi lots of things!
Hey, you know you really don't
have to use my entire name.
I think a simple
"Manager" is enough.
Manager!
That's right.
Manager! Chi calls
this person manager!
Chi remembered it.
Yes, well I'd have to say Mr.
Motosuwa was right on the money.
Common sense would definitely
not be your strongest suit.
Chi.
But there's no question
that you're a very good girl.
Chi is very good girl?
That's right.
Just like what
Mr. Motosuwa said.
He said you were
a very good girl.
Chi is very good girl.
That is what Hideki said.
Well, once again,
thanks for all the hard
work you put in today.
When Chi leaves,
is manager all alone?
Huh?
No other except
Chi is working here?
Well, since you brought it up,
there was someone else before.
A girl actually, but she...
Chi.
Well, nevermind that.
Nevermind?
Oh yeah, there's
just one more thing.
When we finish the
festival, do you think
you'd like to stay on and have
a regular job here at Tirol?
"Do you think you
might like to stay
and have regular job here?"
Really?
If you don't mind...
Please stay.
Chi will go ask
Hideki if it is all right.
Alright then.
So please see if you can come
every week if
he wouldn't... huh?
Thank you, manager!
Wah! Waaah! Ugh...
Manager, are you alright?
Yeah, I'll be fine, Chi,
but it's really not
good to do that.
What is not good?
Is job not good?
Not the job.
I meant hugging people,
that's what.
So it's bad to hug?
Well, it depends
on who, that's all.
Chi does not understand.
Who would be good to hug?
Um, who would? Well...
For instance,
someone you really like.
Someone...
...Chi likes...
If the one that is
meant for me should
one day happen to
fall in love with only me.
That will be the day
when I will have to
part with the one...
Hello there!
Huh?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Is something wrong?
I believe this would
be your chaperone.
Hideki!
Chi passed pastries out!
Call manager "manager."
Invited people in.
Tirol is a bakery.
Good job. Work hard.
Hideki not as tall as Manager.
And Mr. Hiroyasu Ueda,
but call him "manager,"
said he wants Chi
to come back every week.
Hey! Hey! Hold on a sec!
Hideki! Hideki!
Okay, just talk
a little slower. Alright?
I see.
So he asked if you could
keep working there, huh?
Mm!
Well that's great,
good for you, Chi!
Mm. Hideki, can Chi work
more at job at bakery?
Well, of course, if you want to.
Here.
Uh.
So, with that...
Huh?
With that,
Hideki can buy all
the things he wants?
Oh, Chi.
No, this belongs to you, Chi.
Chi?
You worked very
hard for this money,
and it belongs to you.
Hideki means he Hideki
doesn't need money anymore?
Well, it's not like
I don't need it, but...
But?
You see,
it's enough that you
wanted to do that for me
Thank you so much.
Chi.
Go ahead and take it.
This is money you made yourself.
And you deserve it.
I want you to go out and
buy your favorite things.
What are Chi's favorite things?
Well that depends.
Whatever you want to have most.
Hideki...
Hm?
Is it okay if Chi hugs you?
W-What's the matter, asking
me that all of a sudden?
Is it okay?
Uh, sure.
Chi, I'm going to tell you
the rules of the bath house.
Are you ready?
Chi!
First, you pay the fee for
the bath with correct change!
Chi!
Second, you are not allowed
to put the towel
around your waist.
Chi!
Third, no matter
how hot the bath is,
you must not add cold water!
Chi!
Forth, put a towel
on top of your head
when you are in the bath tub!
Chi!
At finally, when you drink a
glass of milk after the bath,
your hand should
be on your waist!
Me-me-me-me-me-
Chi!
The next episode of Chobits:
"Chi buys."
By the way, you can
only drink fruit milk
when you had something
good on that day.