Do you love me?
Or...
That was the worst night's sleep
I think I've ever had.
Just imagining Shinbo
having a relationship
with Miss Shimizu
is driving me nuts.
Ah! I can't stand it!
I'm so jealous of you, Shinbo!
Chi.
But, wait a minute.
I thought that Miss Shimizu
was married, isn't she?
But there's no way
Shinbo could be her husband.
So that means...
He's with someone else's wife?
What's a wife?
What do you mean?
The Sensual Wives at Night.
No, Chi!
You shouldn't read
stuff like that, okay?!
And to answer your question,
a wife is what you call a woman
when she's married to a man.
When she's married?
Huh? Um, well...
It's uh...
Huh?
It's morning!
Time for the
wakey-wakey exercises!
Okay, raise your arms
high up in the air!
What do you think you're doing?!
Scary!
Okay, I'll try it another way:
why are you here, Sumomo?
Here you go.
Please look after
her for a while.
Oh great, and for how long?!
He is scary, he is!
What's going on?
I can't deal with this,
this is totally insane!
5 minutes until departure!
There's never any time;
I just can't handle it!
I'm sorry, Chi!
I'll see you Later!
Chi!
I'm very sorry I'm late;
it won't happen again.
Hey, what's up?
Miss Shimizu
hasn't come in today.
She gets here early
now and then,
but she's never late like this.
Yeah, I hope nothing's wrong.
Miss Shimizu never
did show up in class,
and neither did Shinbo.
I can't seem to get
this out of my mind.
What are they up to?
Chi?
Oh, I wouldn't get too worried;
it'll all sort out somehow.
Chi.
But, that's what I don't get...
Why would Shinbo
just leave Sumomo
with me like that?
Senpai!
Huh?
Senpai, what are
you doing? Watch out!
Huh?
Gah!
Oh my god!
What's the matter with me?!
Is something
bothering you, Senpai?
Well, yeah, I guess
you could sorta...
Huh?
Would you like to make a change?
Because the proceeding event
is running longer than usual,
the show selected
for recording is now
delayed a half hour!
Hey, keep it down, will ya?
Sumomo!
I'm working here;
try to stay quiet?
Do you want me to adjust
the recording time accordingly?
Yeah, okay, sure, whatever.
Just get back into the bag!
Aye!
Shinbo!
Senpai... that Persocom...
Well, you see, I guess Shinbo
just went and put her in my bag
when I wasn't looking,
and now I'm supposed
to look after her
for some reason.
What do you think would have
made him leave her
here with me anyway?
She doesn't take up
much room at all,
and she usually keeps out
of the way most of the time.
Yes, that's very true.
You know a Persocom can
do pretty much anything,
and they can also
do about any job
you could ever want it to do.
I'm sorry, Yumi.
I shouldn't be bothering you
with something like this.
Oh no, don't worry about it!
I'm very happy to be able
to help my senpai
with his problems,
whenever he's in the
mood to share them
with me, that is.
Thank you, that's very nice.
Today was a real disaster.
What a mess;
and it's all because
of Shinbo this time.
Telephone!
Answer, please! Answer, please!
Only five more rings,
and if you don't answer,
I will switch over
to voicemail mode.
All right, go ahead.
Aye! Making connection now.
Hey, what's up?
Wha-?!
Wait a minute!
That sounds like Shinbo's voice!
Where are you?!
And what are you doing?!
I'm eloping with our teacher.
Where do I plug this thing in?
Chi?
I think it was this one.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on...
What's wrong with this thing?!
Come on, let's go now,
show me something!
Chi.
Is this it? This one?
Okay, so this one,
then? This one?
Come on now!
I got it!
Hey, Motosuwa!
Shinbo!
So you managed
to get it hooked up
all by yourself, huh?
I guess I'm a better teacher
than I thought I was.
Enough with the small talk!
What's the deal
with this
"eloping" stuff, Buddy?
What are you doing?!
Just what I said.
I'm currently on the
run with Miss Shimizu.
Well, that's great!
But I wanna know
why you're running off
with a prep school
teacher all of a sudden!
I mean...
How long has this been
going on between you two?
Oh well, it's pretty close
to six months, I'd say.
Are you saying that this started
as soon as we
entered prep school?
Mm-hm!
You and our teacher,
without me ever knowing?!
Chi.
You didn't even tell me!
Well, I didn't think...
Huh?
Oh come on, not now!
Come on!
I guess there's
nothing I can do.
The TV's pretty old,
and it's a cheap
model to begin with,
and I'm sure I don't even
know how to wire up right.
This isn't the time to be
thinking things like that.
What do I do now?!
Hideki...
Chi, I'm gonna go
over to Minoru's house
and see if he
can be of any help.
I'll be right back soon.
You should just
stay right here, okay?
What does eloping mean?
Eh?
Is this good? Or is it bad?
Well Chi, I wish I knew.
That's a tough one. I'm sorry,
but I just don't know
how to answer that.
Hideki.
But I think I'll find out.
Chi.
What's the matter with him,
is he out of his
mind or something?
Eloping with his teacher?
Shinbo, you idiot!
Mr. Motosuwa is here to see you.
What brings him here so late?
I'll go down
and make some fresh
tea for Mr. Motosuwa.
That's quite the
dramatic entrance.
I need you to connect this thing
to a phone line that
can show images!
Can you do that right now?
I presume what you're talking
about is live video feed.
Yeah, I guess it's
something like that.
How do I know?!
That's fine, but who
is it you need to call?
An eloper, that's who!
Huh?
Grrrr.
All right, it's connected now.
So it shows up here?
Yes, after a moment.
So, have you finally you
got it working, Motosuwa?
Shinbo.
Oh, so you're at
Kokubunji's house.
Hello.
All right, that's
enough of that, Shinbo.
Why didn't you
tell me anything?!
I didn't mind
telling you about it.
Huh?
I guess the truth is
I actually wanted
to tell you 'cause...
I really did think of
you as a close friend.
You know what I mean?
I hope you do.
Shinbo...
And I considered you
a close friend too;
that's why I wish
I'd known, that's all.
It's just that
Takako wouldn't say yes.
Takako?
That's Miss Shimizu's
first name.
I don't suppose you know
that Takako was married.
Yeah, I know about that.
She told me about
her husband the night
when she stayed over.
Her husband got hooked
on Persocoms right
after they got married,
and when she noticed,
it seemed like
that was the only thing
they ever talked about.
It didn't happen all at once,
and at the very beginning,
she thought it might even
help bring them together,
so she was happy about
buying a Persocom.
But after a while,
her husband only seemed
interested in the Persocom.
Eventually, it got so bad,
he wouldn't even
bother to talk to her
when she was right there.
With a Persocom?!
You're kidding.
You're still pretty new to this,
that's why it doesn't
mean much to you.
But it's happening
more and more.
Come to think of it...
Do you find
Persocoms attractive?
Is it more fun to be with
a Persocom than a human?
Oh. So that's what
she meant by all that.
You know that little park
near the prep school?
You know the one
with all the trees?
Well, it was right after
the school year started...
It was early evening,
and I was just on my way home
through the park, and Takako...
Of course back at that time,
I wouldn't have even thought
of calling her
by her first name.
But anyway, there she was,
sitting by herself on a swing.
Huh?
She seemed to be
enjoying a private moment,
or getting in tune
with her inner child
or something, so
I just left her alone.
But then, after
I ate some dinner,
and it was getting
pretty late by that point,
I saw her again,
still sitting there.
And that just didn't seem right.
Miss Shimizu?
Oh, Shinbo.
Are you okay?
What are you doing out here?
I can't get in my apartment.
The door's locked,
so I'm sort of stuck here.
So what happened?
Did you lock your keys
inside your house or something?
No, it's not about the keys.
The chain is on,
so I can't get in.
The chain's on?
Then that means there's
someone inside, doesn't it?
Miss Shimizu?
That would be my husband.
Husband?
So, did you have
a fight with him?
A fight?
No, I haven't had a fight
with him in quite a while.
Huh?
Or rather...
we haven't spoken
in quite a while.
Hearing about all that
knocked me for a loop,
so I told her she
ought to be mad at him.
But she just shook her head.
Why?
The fact that he put the chain
on the door means that
my husband has now
completely forgotten that
I would be coming home at all.
I suppose what
it really boils down
to is it doesn't matter
if I'm here or not.
When I thought about it,
nothing seemed
to matter anymore.
Nothing seems to matter.
She said all this,
and yet she wasn't crying,
not a single tear had fallen.
Even though I knew
that deep down
in her heart,
she really wanted to cry.
But she was trying
with all her
might to hold it in.
So, now I'll know,
when bad or cruel
things happen...
that she's able
to cry if she has to.
That was when I fell in love.
And that's when
I started to push the issue.
At first, Takako
kept reminding me
that she was my teacher,
and I was her student,
and of course that
she was married,
and you know, all
those sorts of things.
But I pushed, and I pushed,
and I kept right on pushing.
And that's how we got
to where we are today.
But why'd ya hafta elope,
can you tell me that?!
Is that the only
way you could do it,
is that's what's goin' on?!
First of all, we're still kids!
Didja ever think about that?!
What are you gonna do now?!
It's not gonna be easy!!
Well, I guess ya got a point.
And I know it won't all be
easy; there'll be trouble.
So?
But then again:
this is what I decided,
and it is what it is!
Really? Decided?
Takako has pretty much
lost her trust in men.
So that even if they say
"I love you" at first,
if something that
works to their advantage
or suits their fancy,
like a Persocom, comes along,
they'll just turn
right around as if
nothing ever happened.
And even though I told her
countless times that
I wouldn't be like that,
she didn't believe me.
The other day,
when Takako went
over to your place,
That was the big day.
The two of us were
gonna get together and...
discuss our future.
But when it really
came down to it,
she chickened out
at the last minute.
Well, I guess a woman's
heart is sorta complicated.
That's why...
Why what?
I decided to take her away
to this old hot springs
resort in the mountains
where it's just the two of us.
It's a great place!
Lots of atmosphere.
You're just talking about
a lovey-dovey vacation!
I guess.
But it's still eloping to me.
Anyway, I don't plan
on coming back
until I can finally manage
to get Takako to say yes.
Say yes? To what?
To marrying me.
To marrying you?!
Married. Marriage.
So you're getting married?
That's all, right?
Yeah, so I'd
appreciate it if you can
hold onto Sumomo
a little while longer.
Yeah, I'm sure I could to that.
Who are you talking to?
To Motosuwa.
Oh. Ohhhhh!
Wow, Miss Shimizu is
much sexier than usual!
Okay, see ya, Motosuwa!
I'll give you a call
later when I have a chance.
Hey, wait a minute!
Huh?
Next time, if there's
something going on,
I want you to tell me.
Motosuwa...
I mean, it's not like I could
necessarily do anything;
I couldn't even
get into college.
But I'm not a moron,
and I could have
helped you somehow.
So you... you just...
you have to tell me next time.
Got that?
That's all there is to it!
Sure.
Shinbo.
He's such a big pain.
You know, Motosuwa
really is a nice guy.
Yep, he's one of the best.
But that's also a problem:
he's such a nice guy
that he has a hard
time getting a girlfriend.
And that's why he's a virgin.
That night...
You know, when I stayed
over at Motosuwa's?
Oh, yeah, that would
have been right about
when I was out looking
for you all over town.
I'm so sorry.
But that night...
Huh?
After I had made
such a big fuss,
I was really exhausted...
I woke up and found
Motosuwa leaning
against the wall,
and at that point,
it was hard for me to tell
whether he was
even awake or not.
So that's when,
I just had to ask him.
Do you think it's wrong
for a married person
to fall in love
with someone else?
Not if you can't help it.
Huh?
It's impossible to
control your emotions
when you truly fall in love.
But that kind of situation
is very hard on
everyone involved.
And the whole thing is
very painful for everybody.
So since everybody's suffering,
it's better to follow your heart
and do what's right for you,
than to live in confusion.
That's exactly what he said.
That's awfully wise for Hideki.
Considering he's a virgin.
But there was something
that really affected my heart.
He said everything's all right,
and I should do
what's right for me.
His words made me
feel indescribably calm.
And, so you can
do the right thing,
you're going to be with me, now.
But I haven't said enough yet.
"Yet" just means
that we're moving
in the right direction,
that's all.
Shinbo, you really
are a positive person.
Hold on, now.
So after all we've been through,
I'm still Shinbo to you?
Now, here's a question.
What would I like
you to call me?
Get it right,
and get a gold star!
"Hiromu."
Correct.
Mr. Motosuwa, it's true:
you really are a nice guy.
Oh, I'm not like that at all.
I'm so embarrassed by all this.
But nice guy or not,
you still don't
have a girlfriend.
Ah!
Oh, stop that, willya?!
Leave me alone!
A husband that got hooked
on Persocoms, huh?
Making a real girl cry.
He still prefers a Persocom?
A.
Well done.
B.
Pretty good.
C.
Average.
D.
You're in trouble.
E.
Do better.
F.
Do much, much, better.
G.
Do much, much, much better!
H.
Me!
Huh?
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Provides."
Grumble.
Huh?
No, that was just the
sound of my stomach.