I'm about ready to give up.
I tried everything
I could think of,
but all the Chobits entries
are just a bunch of rumors.
Perhaps you could
save your complaints
for some other time.
Yeah, yeah.
Lord Minoru,
I'm receiving some mail.
It's from that address again.
Send it over.
This is...
Why are you plugged in?
What are you doing, Kotoko?
An analysis.
I am programmed to automatically
analyze anything
regarding Persocoms
that exceeds
regulatory levels, also,
any anomalies that may arise
from special circumstances.
I see, is that so?!
Yes.
Well, Sumomo's programmed to...
Sumomo!
Is programmed to dance
whenever she's on standby!
La la la la la la la la la!
It's just as I thought.
Oh really?
Whatta ya mean,
"just as you thought"?
This apartment has a
peculiar type of connection.
It's "peculiar"?!
Danger, danger!
This is a crisis
situation. Emergency!
This apartment uses an
ultra-fast internet connection:
even large corporations
aren't allowed to use those.
Hideki?
Look, look!
An unidentified object!
Open it; let's examine
the unidentified object!
Chi.
Chi?
I lost the thing that
was most dear to me.
A long time ago, something
very bad happened to me.
It still makes my heart ache.
It made me very, very, very sad.
It was very painful.
It hurt a lot when
I lost something so dear.
But, I am searching.
That is why I am searching.
But, this is...
I just received it.
But where's it from?
Well, I'm not completely
sure about the details,
but, uh, after taking
a little time
and going over the
communication log again,
I think I have a rough idea.
So, who is it?
It's the Persocom data bank.
It's the one Yuzuki had been
attempting to hack, remember?
Data bank?
But what do you mean?
Put it this way: your
Persocom's got some kind
of incredibly valuable
secret deep inside her.
In fact it's gotta be so big
that even the king
of the Persocoms needs
to get this one out of her now.
So that would basically mean...
Well, I'm not so sure about that
from what we know so far.
But if she's not a "chobits,"
then she's an
exceptional Persocom
who's still very much like one.
Oh , I see.
Yeah, a mysterious
custom-made Persocom.
Oh! I'm so jealous!
Hey.
You know, that Persocom is
really way out of your league.
It seems like a real waste
for some ordinary guy
to have such
a genuine treasure
like that Persocom.
You have no idea
how extraordinary she-
Persocom this, Persocom that!
She's got a name, you know;
her name's Chi, okay?!
So don't just treat
her like some thing!
Yeah, I hear you.
They're on the move now.
Well, that's to be expected;
we certainly gave
them enough clues.
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing.
So, Dita.
Have you ever had any
doubts about this mission?
Not really.
We're here to stop a program
that's dangerous to Persocoms.
Even the logic programs
find no contradictions.
I see.
Then, do you have any
idea what kind of danger
could actually
result if that girl
should suddenly
activate her program?
No.
I'm a data bank that carries
all data concerning Persocoms.
And you are a security program
created to protect me.
The two of us are
trying to prevent
that girl from activating
her true program
in order to save all Persocoms.
But then,
we don't really
know what will happen
if that girl does
run her program.
Nor do we know if
it's truly dangerous.
What are you trying to say?
I must remind you of something
about the creator
of the Persocoms:
he feels for all
humanoid Persocoms
as if they were his children.
The data in my memory
is quite clear about this:
parents almost always wish
for the happiness
of their offspring.
So what that girl
possesses might just be
some irresistible
resolve from "him"
for all Persocoms to be happy.
You mean she isn't dangerous?
I didn't say that.
It's just that happiness
for Persocoms
may not be conducive
to happiness for all humans.
I'm not gonna think about it.
That girl is dangerous.
That's why we're gonna stop her.
All right, everybody.
I'm taking off!
Senpai!
U-Um, well I... I mean...
Hm?
I just wanted to
thank you for your help.
I really feel so much
better about myself.
And now I can stop
being so worried
about how I compare to anyone.
That's great, Yumi.
Give it your best shot.
I will, Senpai!
And, you make sure you
keep studying real hard!
You got it!
Well, excuse me,
I have to get back.
Oh, one thing.
Huh?
Well, I know it's strange
to hear me say this, but
I just want to say:
take good care of Chi, okay?
Uh, sure.
Is Chi really a "chobits"?
And if she is, what should I do?
Or more like:
is there anything I can do?
Well, I see you still
talk to yourself too much.
Huh?
Shinbo!
And that's why there's really
nothing I can do for Chi.
Well, that is a bit of a pickle.
But I'd say that before you
start worrying about that,
there's still a
very big question
that you need to clear up.
The really big
question about Chi is:
do you love her?
I don't know.
At least, I'm not
completely sure yet.
But I guess I really do
worry about her an awful lot.
I see.
But can I ask you
something, Shinbo?
Would you hate someone who
fell in love with a Persocom?
Why would I?
Well, you know, I mean
because of Miss Shimizu.
Oh, that.
I getcha now.
Well, when I first heard
about Takako's husband
going off the deep end
and dumping her
for some Persocom,
I gotta admit guys
like that made me sick.
But then, after
I really thought about it,
I came to a
different conclusion.
Different?
Yeah.
I started to wonder
what would have
happened if her
husband was involved
with a human being.
Would it have really
made any difference
if it hadn't been a Persocom?
Would Takako have
been spared any pain?
Would I have been
any less upset?
I didn't dislike guys
who fell in love
with Persocoms; that
really wasn't the problem.
It was guys who took
others for granted,
whether it was a
Persocom or a person.
But, Shinbo.
Wait a sec, you're
not gonna go tell me
that you've got another woman
on your mind, are you buddy?
No, of course not!
Then it's not a problem.
I certainly wouldn't stop ya.
I am me, that's who I am.
And I am it, that's who I am.
I am myself.
I am not human.
But still...
All the more...
to love me because I am me.
I can love because that
person is that person.
The One Just for Me.
Chi?
Hideki.
Oh, I'm back, Chi.
Welcome back, Hideki.
Oh, well I see the place
is still as empty as ever.
Oh! Hey, Sumomo!
Are you doin' all right?
Aye! Sumomo's as
energetic as always!
Do you think the
two of you could stay
with Shinbo for a little while?
Hey, nice to meet you.
Hm, you seem more normal
than Mr. Motosuwa.
It's very nice to meet you.
Excuse me for not being normal.
Well, we'll just be getting out
of your hair for a little while.
But make sure you take
the time to talk to her.
Talk? What should I talk about?
To start with,
I guess I'm not really
all that sure just
how I feel about Chi.
Am I really
so confused about this?
Maybe I just haven't
thought it through yet.
Hideki?
Hideki, is something wrong?
Does it hurt somewhere?
Oh, Chi.
Hideki, why are you
holding Chi this way?
I... I don't know, myself.
Ugh.
Zima!
What's the matter?!
Another intruder?
No, it's just that there
was too much data just now.
Not yet, Dita,
hold off for a minute.
What are you talking about?!
What's gonna happen to you
if all your data crashes, Zima?!
If I crashed, all I'd have
to do is re-enter the data.
We are Persocoms,
after all, right?
Yeah, that's true, but...
Zima!
That girl!
She's around here!
That girl is around
here, isn't she?!
No, Dita.
I've gotta get over there!
This can't wait another minute.
I've gotta stop that program!
Well, the cat's out of the bag,
and there's no
way to stop it now
if the fact is that
I want that girl...
...to be happy.
Chi?
I'm sorry.
Hideki.
Mr. Motosuwa.
Miss Hibiya!
There's something
important I've really
wanted to ask you
about, Miss Hibiya.
I know.
Huh?
I think it's time
I told you everything...
about Chi, I mean.
Please.
Thank you.
This way.
Uh...
It's down here.
What is this place?
It's something that
my husband made.
In addition to the system
for humanoid Persocoms.
Huh?!
Why do you have
this, Miss Hibiya?
Hey, wait a minute,
isn't that...?!
Yes, you're right.
That's me in the picture.
It was taken quite a while ago;
that was in the lab
where we used to work.
And next to me is Elda.
Elda?
That's right.
You see, back then,
she used to be called Elda.
But at the moment,
she's known as:
Chi.
And there's one more
I must tell you about.
The one called Freya.
Huh? What do you mean,
"one more"?
Are you trying to
say this one isn't Chi?
That's right. The two
of them are different.
So...
Allow me to explain.
You see, Elda and Freya
were sort of like children
that my husband made
especially for me.
Cute little girls
that he built for me,
because I wasn't able
to have any children.
The first one to
be built was Freya.
One day, I was called over
to the lab and there she was.
She opened her eyes
and smiled at me.
Mama.
I was so happy.
We all lived together,
and as time went by,
she started to learn
various things on her own,
little by little.
And she grew up to
be a very sweet girl.
My husband poured all of
his technical expertise
as well as his love
into creating Freya.
So that she would
be a being to love.
And also a being
that would fall in love.
So the person who
took this photo...
...was my husband.
We loved our Freya very much,
and she had found
someone to love.
But then, I couldn't
see her true feelings.
I didn't realize who
she was in love with.
I was worried about Freya being
so melancholy all of the
time, so after a while,
I asked my husband to create
a little sister for her.
That was Elda,
whom you call Chi.
Freya seemed so happy
now that she had
a younger sister.
But there were
still these odd times
when she looked
like she was thinking
very deeply about something.
She had fallen in love with him,
but she used all
of her willpower
to keep her heart locked up.
Then one day,
Freya could no longer
stand the pain, and she...
It wasn't until then
that I finally realized
who Freya had
fallen in love with.
And that person was
my husband, you see.
The lab technicians working
with us on the project suggested
that we erase all
of Freya's memories.
But to my husband,
that wasn't an option.
And after that, Freya
just chose to disappear.
However, the same
system had been
integrated into Elda,
and she remained with us.
The lab technicians
feared that the same thing
would happen, and they
wanted to get rid of Elda.
But my husband wouldn't
hear of that either.
Time passed, and an
illness took my husband.
So I reformatted Elda
so that she'd be able
to find someone dear
to her on her own.
And that's when I...
Chi is very dangerous to them.
Or rather... it's not just that
Chi's so dangerous to them,
she's dangerous
to all Persocom users.
Dangerous?
But...
You are the one Mr. Motosuwa...
who will decide.
Darling. This was the
right thing to do, wasn't it?
It's not just that
it's wrong, it's absurd...
that something so truly loved,
and that's trying
to love a human,
can't find happiness.
It's only fair that
Persocoms should have
the right to be happy too.
That's what you always said.
You created Chi
because you wanted
to find true happiness.
The happiness of
humans and Persocoms.
And that's why
I will see this
through to the very end.
I must do this,
so that Chi can be happy.
I can tell.
I am you, you are me.
That's why I know.
One person fills
me up completely.
I'm happy when
that person laughs.
I'm happy when that
person is by my side.
Yes, I'm happy when
that person is happy.
He's different from the others,
this person is special.
You found him. My dearest...
My special...
The One Just for Me.
I hope he finds me.
Just as I found him,
and then fell in love
because he was who he was.
I hope he finds me.
Things that I can do
because I am me,
and things that I can't
do because I am me.
I hope he finds them, and...
I hope he falls in love
with me because I am who I am.
From amongst all those
people and things...
I want him to find me.
I want him to fall
in love with me.
But...
If he cannot find me...
Chi.
Chi, I- I uh...
Hideki.
Are you The One
that is Just for Me?
I, uh...
Chi is in love with Hideki.
Is Hideki in love with Chi?
Chi, I...
This is the...
Was it really all right
to take this time off?
Hm?
Hey, what's the matter?
It's a voice.
What is it? Is something wrong ?
Yuzuki!
Miss Sumomo!
Hm?
That voice again.
Uh, what is it?
Hey, come on, you two,
what's going on?
Hey!
Chi.
This town is full of people...
and full of them.
All sorts of people...
and all sorts of them...
live in all sorts of places.
Falling in love with someone,
being loved by someone.
Among lots of people
and lots of them,
I have found...
Next episode of Chobits:
"The One Just for Chi."
I want that person
to find it, too.