Chi.
Oh, are you up, Chi?
This room really gets
bright in the mornings.
I've been thinking,
maybe I should buy some
curtains to shut out the light.
Good morning, Hideki.
That's great!
You've got all the
greetings down, Chi!
Chi remembers
lots of other things.
Things that Hideki taught me.
Electric light.
That's right.
Television.
Correct!
Yummies.
Absolutely!
More yummies.
Yeah. Well...
In a way I guess
you're right, uh...
Not yummies?
Well, it's not
that you're wrong...
Hm? What's the matter, Chi?
You really don't seem
like yourself today.
Aren't you feeling well?
Feeling well?
"Feeling well" is not
something Chi has learned yet.
Let's see.
It could mean that
your head sorta hurts,
or your stomach's upset,
or you've got
pains in your chest.
Head?
It doesn't look like it.
Stomach?
You're fine.
Chest?
No, you're just fine.
I can see that!
Hey, Motosuwa!
I've got an appointment today,
so I'm going in early!
I'm going in early!
I wonder what's up
with Shinbo today.
Aw, where's my head?
I should've asked Shinbo
about you just now, Chi.
I'm so dumb.
I guess I'll ask
him later at school.
Ah! I better hurry,
or I'm gonna be late!
I gotta go now, Chi.
I'm afraid it's time for me
to head out to school myself.
I'll talk to Shinbo about you,
and be right back after work.
Take care of yourself.
I'm gonna be late.
I'll come back home
as soon as I can, okay?
Stay here,
and I'll see you later.
Chi.
Oh, what's this?
Oh no, "Final notice."
The phone bill and
the electric bill?
But I'm not getting
paid until this Friday!
Good morning, Mr. Motosuwa.
Oh, g'morning!
Uh--
Gotta go!
The Ashikaga shogunate
lost its power at that time.
So, with the
importation of firearms,
the Middle Ages of
Japan comes to an end,
and Nobunaga takes his
place to open the doors
of the modern age in terms
of politics and economics.
Therefore, if you're going
to open the classroom door,
I'd also appreciate it if you
would close it, Mr. Motosuwa.
Ab-absolutely! Good morning!
Rather than waiting,
we started without you.
Yes. I'm late. I'm sorry.
Ten laps around the track!
Huh?
Go on!
Right!
Hey, I was kidding.
It's just a joke.
Eh?
Do you really mean it?
Do you see a running track
anywhere in this building?
Uh.
But because you
played along so well...
Hm?! Oh.
I'm gonna let you off
the hook this time.
Now, you better take your seat.
I'm going to call on you a lot!
Huh?
But I thought you were
gonna let me off the hook?
You were even later than usual.
Are you having another
problem of some sort?
That's right.
I really want your opinion on
something a little later on.
Mr. Motosuwa, page
forty-three of the textbook.
Uh, right!
Your Persocom's acting strange?
Sorta.
I haven't really
had any problems
with her up 'til now,
but this morning it seemed
like she wasn't responding
to much of anything.
She seemed lethargic,
almost like you feel
when you catch a cold.
Uh, I don't get it.
So what do you think
I'm doing wrong now?
Are you re-charging her?
Huh?
You're not
charging her, are you?
What do you mean charging her?
Shouldn't she charge herself?
You know, we are talking about
electrical appliances here!
Do you think they'd
just go out somewhere
and soak up some voltage
without consent of the owner?!
Well I guess that's true.
That "girl" is just a Persocom!
Right. Yeah.
Okay, first thing,
you don't take it
outside much, do you?
Well, I'm busy with
work every afternoon.
And I'm not sure if I want Chi
to be walking around by herself.
It was a huge mess just to
get her some underpants.
Hey, Sumomo.
It's time for a lesson.
Can you please tell Motosuwa
how to recharge a
Persocom's batteries.
Yes, sir! Request understood.
Persocoms use their
onboard solar arrays
to partially recharge
their batteries merely
by taking them
outside into the sunlight.
The power to perform
most everyday chores
can be achieved by
self-generating energy
using this method.
However, if conditions
prevent a Persocom
from utilizing direct sunlight
for a long period of time...
...the alternative method is
by using this charging cord!
In most cases this cord
is conveniently located
somewhere in the head region.
I see! That thing in her ear...
I'll bet anything you don't
have a power adapter, either...
Well no. Not really.
Okay, how many amps you use?
I don't know.
Now be careful.
If you do a complete
quick-charge
to full capacity,
it'll be a big pull.
I fixed my place up so
it's all right, but...
Now where...
Oh, here it is. Here y'go.
Just try charging her up,
and if she still
doesn't seem right,
I'll take a look at her.
This is great. You saved me!
Thanks, Shinbo.
Mmm. What to do
about work today...
I'm really worried
about Chi's condition.
I wonder if I could manage
to take the day off.
Motosuwa Senpai!
Uh?
I finally caught up with you!
Boy, I'm glad I didn't
let you get away.
I ran all the way to catch you!
Yumi!
You're, uh, working
today, aren't you?
Later this afternoon?
Oh, yeah...
About my work
schedule today- Oh!
Wow!
This is the first time I've seen
Yumi in her school uniform.
Senpai?
Huh?
Is this really the first time
you've seen my school uniform?
Aggh! Not again!
Was I talking out loud?
So what do you think of it?
Our uniform's pretty popular!
Um. So then.
Getting back to the subject
of today's schedule.
Oh yeah, right,
today's schedule.
Well, one of our other
employees can't make it today,
so instead of my regular shift,
I have to go in early.
Everyone else needs to pitch in!
Um, yeah.
I was supposed to have
my club meeting today, too.
Our pub works
really hard, doesn't it?
C'mon, Senpai,
let's go and complain.
I can't do it.
I just can't skip work today.
Good afternoon, welcome.
Have a seat anywhere.
Yumi, two drafts for
counter number seven!
My pleasure!
I'll take these plates.
Two drafts, coming up!
Wow, it was really busy today.
Thanks for all the
hard work, Senpai!
Same to you, Yumi. See ya!
Bu- Sure. G'nite.
Chi, I'm back home.
Chi!
Chi! Are you all right?! Chi!
Hideki.
I'm really sorry, Chi.
But there's nothing
to worry about.
I'll get you
charged up right away!
Okay then,
I've got it all set up!
Here we go, Chi!
Aagghhhh!!
Huh?
Eh? Eh?
Huh!
What? What is it?
What's going on?
What in the world
is going on here?!
It's not... a blackout.
Is it really just
because of this?
Hideki.
Hideki, welcome home.
Chi.
Chi, are you alright?
Is Chi alright?
Calm down now. Think, think!
Now be careful.
If you do a complete
quick-charge
to full capacity,
it'll be a big pull.
That's it!
I just blew the circuit breaker!
Just a minute, I'll have you
back to normal right away.
Wait a sec!
Why aren't the
lights coming back on?
Isn't flipping this
thing is supposed
to bring back the power!
I guess it really is broken!
Shinbo!
Are you sleeping?! Shinbo!
Oh no, he's not back
from school yet...
Miss Hibiya! It's Motosuwa!
I'm really sorry it's
so late! Miss Hibiya?
Of course, she would be gone
now as well, wouldn't she?
I've got to reach someone.
If Shinbo's not around,
maybe Kokubunji...
Uh?
No! It can't be out of order!
Oh no! The final due
date for the phone bill
was supposed to be today!
Which could also mean
that the due date for
the electric bill was-
Just as I thought.
But what I need now is a phone!
Was there a pay
phone around here?
This... is all I've got.
Wal-let.
Hm?
This is a wallet.
This is bag.
Is it correct?
Yeah. It's correct.
Good girl, Chi.
Chi has learned many things.
Hideki has taught
many things to Chi.
It's all right. Just rest.
You don't have to talk.
It'll be all right. I'll do
something about this.
I'll make sure
I do something about it.
So you don't have to
talk anymore, okay?
"My Pleasure"
is open until 2:00am.
Someone must still be there.
Huh?!
Chi?
I-It's nothing.
Hold on, Chi,
you just hold on tight!
Chi.
All right, here we go!
Chi is heavy?
Oh no, you're lighter than
when I first picked you up.
It'll be faster if
I cut through there.
Under construction?!
No way! I don't
have time to think!
Let's see... Which way?
All right... So we're here.
Turn left when we
get to that mailbox.
It looks like we've
got a little detour.
That's the building!
Hey, we did it, Chi!
"My Pleasure" is right
near that building!
There's no time
to walk around it.
Chi.
It's just on the
other side of that.
Do you think you
can make it, Chi?
Yes, Chi can make it.
We made it! Chi, we made it!
Unh...
Hideki.
Chi, are you all-
Hey, Chi... Talk to me!
Chi! Are you alright?
Chi, hang in there!
Chi what's wrong?
Chi... Chi!
Wait just a minute;
I'm gonna get you there!
Dammit, she's
getting heavy again!
Mr. Motosuwa?
M-Miss Hibiya?!
Yes.
Uh, bu- umm... How did you-?
Well, while I was
looking out the window,
I saw someone tumbling down.
So I asked him to stop.
The window?
Yes, from the taxi cab window.
Were you heading home?
I'd actually hoped to get
home much earlier than this,
but there were simply too
many errands I had to run.
Well, you really saved me.
I don't know what
I would've done
if you hadn't passed by,
Miss Hibiya.
Oh, now, please don't overreact.
I'm not overreacting. I mean it.
In fact, you're the one who
saved both of us, Miss Hibiya.
All I did was run around
and put us in danger.
Hideki.
Chi.
Are you all right, Chi?
Hideki.
Oh thank goodness.
You should be
all right now, Chi.
When you feel better,
you can say thank you
to Miss Hibiya.
Warm.
Hideki is warm. Very warm.
Chi is happy.
Chi.
Oops!
You're a lifesaver.
I'll pay for the electricity
I'm using right now.
Oh, don't worry
about it, please.
I won't have it any other way.
I can't just expect you
to fix every single thing
that goes wrong in
my life, you know!
Well, now, really.
I don't think I did all that-
Hm?!
Hey there!
Shinbo.
Mr. Shinbo, welcome home.
Motosuwa, hey man,
what are you guys doing?
I'm, recharging Chi.
Recharging?
Yow! Oh man, that's fast!
Hey Motosuwa!
The electric meter is going
around at an amazing speed!
An amazing speed?
At this rate, you're gonna
have to get another job!
Really?!
Do Persocoms always
use that much power?
Well, I've never seen anything
like this with a
Persocom before.
I'm really sorry.
I promise to pay you
back for every single watt.
But do you think you can wait
until the end of the month?
Don't worry about it,
the electricity's no problem.
But aside from that,
I've been meaning
to have a conversation with you
about the rent for this month.
Gah!
The rent! No! Did I-
Well, I haven't
received your check yet.
Okay.
I promise I'll bring
you the rent
just as soon as I get
paid at the restaurant.
Please forgive me!
Chi?
I'll make sure to have
it for you by Friday!
Even if I have
to work myself to death,
I'll make sure I have the money!
Oh, please don't worry
about it so much!
I don't mind when you pay it,
just as long as you do pay it.
I can't do that!
I promise you,
I'll bring you the rent
and the electricity
money by Friday.
Really, don't worry
about it so much!
Chi?
You know, most
people seem to have
a pretty hard time
losing weight,
but somehow you never
seem to get any fatter.
I got paid the other day,
and I thought I'd finally
gotten you back to average size,
but you just withered away
in less than an instant!
I mean, I'm doing my best here,
so can you at least
try not to get so thin?
Hideki. Who are you talking to?
My wallet.
The next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Works."
It's really hard to
make money, isn't it?