Okay, for utility bills,
I'll have electricity,
gas, water.
Food should cost
about that much.
And then there's transportation,
the phone bill, and rent.
Hmmm...
I guess I'll need
about 70,000 yen
And then that means,
if I can work four hours
a day, 6 days a week,
that's over 700 yen per hour.
Oh wait, I've gotta
buy schoolbooks, too.
And then with
miscellaneous expenses,
I'm gonna have to make
at least 800 yen an hour.
Chi.
My puny little savings will
be gone inside of a month.
Worse than that, I might
not be able to make the rent!
I've gotta find a job soon!
Chi.
Hmm?!
Calm down! Must remain calm.
She's just a Persocom.
She just wants to see
my bank book, that's all!
That's all, nothing more!
Chi.
Her breasts... so soft.
Motosuwa!
Huh?
Oh, sorry.
Already busy so
early in the day?
Ya idiot, I was just--
I mean, it's not like that!
Yeah, right, whatever;
but it's time.
You are coming to
class with me, aren't ya?
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I'll be right down.
Okay, I'll wait
downstairs, see ya.
Sure.
All right, I have to go now.
Chi.
Oh, it'll be okay.
I won't be gone too long,
I'll be back by tonight.
Chi!
Just a minute.
Whenever people leave
for a little while,
you don't say
"Chi" to them, say:
"Take care of yourself."
Chi.
Tay- Tay care uh...
"Take care of yourself."
Take care of yourself.
Right!
So when someone's
going out, you say:
"Take care of yourself."
Take care of yourself.
I'm Hideki.
You understand?
Hi... deki.
Right! Hideki!
Hideki!
That's right, Chi!
Hideki.
All right!
That's right!
Hideki.
Oh really?
Hideki. Hideki. Hideki. Hideki.
Hideki. Hideki.
No, that's not it;
you got it all wrong!
I didn't think teaching
was going to be this hard.
Can I really do it?
Mr. Motosuwa.
Huh?
Miss Manager!
Good morning!
And a good morning to you, too.
Is it your first day
of classes today?
Yes.
Well, give it your best, then.
Thanks.
She's as pretty as always today.
It's so soothing.
Take care of yourself.
Right. Well, time to go.
Great!
Yeah, I can see it's definitely
gonna be a good day today!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
He's awfully bright-eyed
and bushy-tailed.
Hideki.
Not that way, Hideki!
You're supposed
to get in the front!
So are junior high kids
all like that these days?
They've all got Persocoms.
I'd love to be back in
junior high kid again.
So tell me, how'd you
happen to meet Minoru?
Oh, it was on a really
cool internet site.
We were both posting on a forum
for custom-made Persocoms.
It just started from there,
and we've been swapping
e-mails ever since.
So what's up?
Was he able to
help you figure out
anything about your Persocom?
Even four of his Persocoms
and then another
one weren't enough.
What he was able
to do is to figure out
that she's definitely
a custom-made Persocom.
And she's got a
learning program installed,
which seems like a good thing.
Apparently she's
also something called,
"protected," but he doesn't
know all the details about that.
You're one lucky farmboy
to stumble onto such
a powerful Persocom.
There aren't a lot of
custom-made Persocoms
that could fry that
many of Kokubunji's!
Well, if there's anything
else you need to know,
feel free to ask
either one of us.
Give us a call;
we're more than
happy to help out.
I appreciate that.
Oh yeah, is your Persocom okay?
I was waiting for
you to ask me that.
Her circuits were
all messed up, big time.
It took a whole night to
get her back like before.
Hey, Sumomo!
Well that's a huge relief.
I was kinda worried about
the next time I'd see you
and what I would say if
you weren't able to fix her.
Aye!
I wouldn't let my little
Sumomo stay like that!
I've put too much time
and money into her!
It's a good thing I was careful
and backed up all her data.
If I had to buy new parts
I woulda charged you for 'em.
I don't have any money.
You'd find a way to pay.
You're a fiend.
You know it.
So, if any of her components
were to get broken,
how expensive are
the replacements?
Um, well, um, that depends on...
Hey, Sumomo!
Aye!
How much does your
memory go for these days?
I'll do a search on the web.
What do you mean by: "memory"?
I have a few hits.
Here.
Aye.
Wow! That's amazing.
I didn't know that Persocoms
could write by hand.
You bet.
Course a printer
can also be attached.
Then why do you have her
write by hand like that?
She just looks
cute when she writes.
Huh, well that's kinda weird.
Is she really serious?
Yep, that's about right.
Do you have any
idea how many weeks
I could live off of
that kinda money?
Persocoms tend to have
big appetites for money.
Luckily, you don't
know about all that yet.
But as you start to get upgrades
and other software you want,
you're gonna wind
up spending quite a lot.
I'm not really sure
what you're talking about,
but I can tell it's
gonna be pretty rough.
I was lucky enough to
find a cute computer,
but I'm just struggling to
get by and get into college.
Can I really deal with her?
That's it.
I'm gonna have
to find a job today.
All right, now everyone,
please take your seats!
Good Morning, my
name's Takako Shimizu.
I'll be your teacher
for the rest of the term.
I will be teaching you
Japanese literature, math,
and English composition.
It's nice to meet you all.
Miss Takako Shimizu, huh?
Wow, another pretty woman.
Now then, first of all,
before getting started,
I'd like to take just a
minute to take roll call!
What's that all about?
Doesn't she trust us?
Roll call?
This isn't grade school ya know.
Indulge me!
As a matter of fact,
the truth is I wanted
to be an elementary
school teacher.
So answer cheerfully when
you hear your name called.
Let's get started, all right?
First up, Asaoka.
Here.
Imai.
There's something
really cool about her.
Boy, if somebody like her
taught elementary school,
I wouldn't mind starting
school all over again.
Motosuwa, you need to put
a little more effort
into it than that.
Okay.
Motosuwa, come on,
even a baby can jump over that!
Wow, Motosuwa,
that's really good,
you're quite an artist!
Motosuwa...
Motosuwa... Motosuwa...
Motosuwa! Motosuwa!
And where were you just now?
Oh, hi there.
You know, if you spend your days
in class like that,
you'll be wasting a lot of time.
Uh, yes Miss Shimizu.
Okay, I'm gonna shoot
for 100,000 yen a month.
And if possible,
close to my apartment.
Hey, there's a
couple of listings.
All right!
Today's my day.
This is day I get a job!
When money's the thing
you're so worried about...
Make some!!
To end poverty, and to
have more computer time!
Nothing can stop me now!
Mommy, look!
Come on honey!
Just pretend you don't see him.
Hideki!
Oh, this is the place.
Excuse me!
Back here!
Uh, hi, it said that you
were hiring part-time.
Oh, I'm sorry, we
already found somebody.
Oh, I see.
Sorry.
N-no, that's fine, I'll just
try somewhere else.
No problem!
Excuse me!
We're done hiring.
I'm pretty sure
I'm strong enough!
I'm sorry, but...
I'll work as hard as you need.
We only hire girls.
I'll do anything!
Do you need a part-time job?
Ooh, you're cute.
I might have
something for you to do.
Uhh, I-I think I'm
in the wrong place.
Ah, boy.
Man, how'd it get so
late all of a sudden?
I never knew the world
was such a tough place,
I guess I'd better
get used to it.
It must be the recession.
But I guess,
if I stay like this,
I shouldn't even
have come to Tokyo.
If I don't find something soon,
I can forget about a Persocom!
Well alright then,
so I can't pick
and choose my work anymore.
Even if nothing's around here,
I swear I'll find it somewhere.
I don't know how
or where, but...
Hm?
What is this?
Ah, oh my goodness.
I'm so sorry!
I musta totally spaced
out or something!
Oh no, it's okay
don't worry about it,
I'm gonna be fine.
I can't just let you
walk away like that;
it wouldn't be right!
Geez, I'm such a
klutz sometimes.
Come on.
My hand.
Really, I'm so sorry.
Please, just let me fix you up.
Huh?
Come on, come on.
Hey, wait a minute, I...
I'm really sorry about this,
but do you mind wearing
wear those for a little while?
I'll get these dry cleaned
for you right away.
Oh no, you don't really
have to go to all that.
Then if you don't mind,
I'll just use an iron
to dry them out.
Please, have a seat
while I take care of it.
Be right back!
Um, uh--
I really don't mind.
Just take a second!
But you don't --
Well, who'd have expected this?
But ya gotta admit,
she's pretty cute!
Her hand was so soft.
Perhaps the flowers
of love will bloom
from this, the very day
of our first meeting.
Mr. Motosuwa!
Oh no. Wait, what is it?
Oh, that was lame.
I should have at least
asked her what her name was.
Hey, isn't anybody here?
What's going on?
Hey, Yumi!
I need you to
help out for a bit!
Aw, man!
I'm never gonna
get all this done.
Uh, excuse me.
Oh, it's a Japanese pub.
Huh?
A Persocom hooked
to the register.
Wow, it's just amazing
the things you can do
with a Persocom.
I wonder if Chi'll be able
to do things like that?
Oh, ah, my pants got all soaked,
and well, don't be
suspicious, 'cause...
While I was waiting
for my clothes
to get dried, I heard someone...
Uh.
These clothes...
I guess you're wondering
how I got them.
Well that's better,
there's someone to help me.
Where were you
when it was so busy?
Hurry up, or we're not gonna
make it in time to open!
Come on!
Huh? Oh, sure.
Hey, so you ready to go yet?
Yeah we're just about, Boss!
Great.
I'm sure you'll work
as hard as usual.
Hm?
Oh yeah, I like him;
this new guy works like a dog.
He's a real keeper.
Excuse me.
Huh? Yes? May I help you?
So, who are you?
Oh.
Oh, so you were
here in the restaurant!
I was looking all over for you!
Ah, Yumi...
What's the matter, Dad?
Um...
Hey, well, sorry about all that.
Didn't mean to
startle you back there.
Seems one of the
employees got the idea
you're the new part-time guy.
Uh, what was it...?
Oh, it's Motosuwa sir.
Ah right, Motosuwa.
I apologize for the
misunderstanding.
Me too, I'm really sorry
I splashed water on you before.
Oh no, really,
it's not a big deal.
Don't worry about it.
Everything's fine.
Well thank you;
that's very nice of you.
Say, since I got ya here;
are you a student?
Uh.
Yeah, as a matter of fact I am.
I'm at a college prep school.
Huh...
Don't suppose you're
looking for work?
Oh-well-I-uh...
Well-uh, actually I am.
Although I seem to
be having a rather hard
time finding anything
right at the moment.
Hmm...
So, those clothes
you're wearing right now.
Tell me, whatta ya think of 'em.
Ya like the way they feel?
Sure.
Yeah, they got
a good cut to 'em.
You don't look half-bad either.
How'd ya like to
wear 'em for a while?
Huh?
How'd ya like to work
part-time for us for real?
I guess is what
I'm trying to get at.
Huh?
You're not serious, are you?!
Sure.
Yeah, actually, I need a guy.
One of my part-time boys just
quit and I've got an opening.
I've been asking
my daughter Yumi
to work here after
high school lets out,
but it's still not enough,
I need more help.
Yes!
Just in time!
I really need to earn a whole
lot of money as fast as I can!
And I promise you that
I'll work real hard sir!
Well that's music to my ears,
so I guess it musta been
a case of good timing.
I'm sure you'll be a first-rate
employee, young man.
It's my pleasure!
Well, isn't that nice.
You already learned the
name of our little place.
Huh?
You've already
memorized the name!
That's the actual name
of our restaurant,
it's called: "My Pleasure"!
A-ha.
Oh, that's why. I see.
Excuse me boss,
we need you out here.
Okay, I'm coming.
Oh, right.
There's one more thing.
I don't suppose you
can bring me in a resume.
It's just a little formality,
if ya don't mind.
Yes, sir!
Well I guess I'll be seeing
you on a regular basis, hm?
All right, I did it!
I actually found a job!
It's gonna work out;
I'm gonna survive!
Good-bye poverty!
And hello Persocom!
You'll be happy, Chi!
Chi?
Huh?! Oh, yeah.
That's the name of my Persocom.
Oh, wow, I didn't know,
so you have your own Persocom?
Oh yeah, I do.
Well to be honest,
I sort of found it.
Really?
Where'd you find
something like that?
In the garbage.
That's strange.
You think it was an older model?
I have to admit I really
don't have the slightest idea.
And speaking of Persocoms,
I noticed that the restaurant
also seems to have one.
That's true.
So, um Yumi,
I guess you probably
have a Persocom, too, don't you?
Yeah, take a look,
it's right here.
Huh? What's that?
Is that a Persocom?
That's right.
It's my very own
mobile Persocom.
It's got its limits,
but it handles most
smaller applications.
I can receive e-mail,
and it's really handy
for a lot of simple things,
like calculations
and memos and stuff.
Oh, that reminds me,
my resume's in here, also.
Oh!
Huh?
Since you happen to mention it,
I've never written a
resume in my whole life.
I worked on the farm,
helped my folks,
and did lots of chores.
Oh, that's funny,
I never thought of it.
I guess I've never
actually worked
anywhere but the farm.
Oh, wow, I see.
Would you like me to teach you
how to put one together then?
Do you really mean it?
That would be great!
If you're sure it's not
too much trouble.
It's my pleasure!
So do you understand the basics?
Uh, yeah...
Oh, that's interesting,
so your family has
a farm in Hokkaido?
That's so cool.
Well it's not the biggest farm
you've ever seen,
but we call it home.
Okay, now that space,
that's for your
educational info.
And that's pretty
much all there is to it!
I just can't thank you enough.
Yumi, you're a lifesaver.
Oh, that's quite all right,
I'm happy to help when I can.
Any time Motosuwa-senpai!
Senpai?
Didn't ya hear me?
Motosuwa-senpai.
How did I suddenly
get to be your senpai?
Think about it.
You're older than me,
so even though
were not classmates,
you're my senpai in life.
So that means I call you
"Motosuwa senpai"!
Uh.
Well, if you say so,
I guess it must be true.
What can I say.
Boy oh boy, these
high school girls
are something these days.
I'm a D cup.
Gah?
Whaaaa--?!
Hey now just a cotton
pickin' minute here!
Did I say something that
I don't remember sayin'?!
Well, you were staring at them.
Well, it's not like
I was thinking about...
or thinking in any kinda
way about... or that...
Not at all?
Not even a little?
Well, I'd be lying
if I said I wasn't
at all or wasn't
thinking about that,
but it really wasn't
like that kinda "that",
it's just, well, they were,
I mean they are such-well,
of course I-oh, I'm so confused.
Gee senpai, you sure are cute.
M-my pleasure.
I wonder if she was
just making fun of me.
Aw, who cares anyway?
I found a job,
and Yumi's really cute.
Hello, I'm home!
Chi!
Chi.
Hey, are you really that happy?
Take care of yourself.
No Chi.
That's not what you're
supposed to say now.
That's what you say
when someone's leaving.
At times like this,
you're supposed to say
"Welcome home."
You say "Wel-come"
Wel- welcome home.
That's it, Chi. Good job!
Welcome home!
Boy, it's hard to
believe sometimes
just how cute you are.
Well I'm glad you're happy, Chi!
You know what I did today?
I found myself a job!
Found a- found a job?
That's right, well,
you see, a job is...
Hmmm...
How do I explain it?
Well, in any case,
things are looking better;
I'll be able to buy
you lots of things,
so you please don't worry.
Chi, don't worry?
Yep, that's right.
Are you happy, Chi?
Happy? Happy.
That's right, that's right.
"Ha-Happy"?
Chi does not understand.
Well "happy" is sort of like...
Let me see... when
your face looks like this.
Happy... Happy.
That's it, Chi,
that's what it means.
That's happy.
And I promise, I'll do
my very best for you.
Okay, now it's
time for some food.
Right as I was leaving,
the manager came over
and gave me this.
He said he hoped things
weren't too bad at home.
Chi, would you get
that for me, please?
Hideki!
Uh.
Well, I guess I really
oughta teach her
that pointing at something
doesn't mean "Hideki."
Hideki!
Uh, you know, Chi...
What I'm trying
to say is: I'm Hideki.
Hideki!
Now that I've got
a part time job,
it looks like I'll be able
to handle all my expenses, Chi!
Chi.
Now, we can buy various things.
Various?
Yeah, like study guides,
curtains, and CDs.
I can buy all the things
I've ever wanted!
Chi!
But, I can't buy the one thing
that Chi needs the most.
Chi needs the most.
Chobits.
Next episode: "Chi's Errand."
Since Chi is an
electronic appliance,
why can't they
sell her underwear
in the appliance section?!