Welcome, come on in!
Right this way, please.
Here ya go: two beers!
Okay, order up over here!
Why was Yumi out
there that night?
She seemed to
know Mr. Ueda, too.
What was that all about?
Excuse me!
I'd like to order now,
if you don't mind.
Hello?
Oh, yes. It's my pleasure!
Here ya go.
Also, some yakitori
and a plate of sashimi.
Oh, right! It's my pleasure!
Hm, still not here.
I wonder what's going
on with Miss Hibiya.
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Hideki.
Welcome back.
Hey, everybody.
Thanks for taking
care of the place.
When you hear the
sound of the stomach,
it means it's time to eat!
No, not now.
Tonight, I think it's more
important that I study.
Do you mean to
say that you intend
to skip a meal, even
though you're hungry?
So what you really mean is
you don't have any money.
Now how did I know that?
Hideki's money is gone?
Then Chi will cook again
using her money from Tirol!
Chi wants to see Hideki smile.
Chi.
Chi?
Yeah, so I found this
really great place.
Really?
Yeah, I'm sure you're
gonna love this restaurant.
It's got nice atmosphere,
and of course,
the food's incredible.
That sounds great; I'm starved!
So what kind of food is it?
Oh, it's a combination
of Russian and...
Chi? What's the matter?
Hideki why are those people
shaking hands like that?
Oh, they're not shaking hands.
They're holding hands.
Why do they hold hands?
Oh, well, because they like it,
and they feel happy
when they do it.
Happy?
So you can feel happy
if you hold hands with someone?
Well not just with anyone.
You see, it only works
with somebody you love.
Happy holding hands.
Here we are.
Let's go in.
Hello there!
Anybody here?
Huh, that's weird.
I wonder why
there's nobody around.
Are you back there? Mr. Ueda?
Oh, there you are.
Uh? Wha...? Oh, Motosuwa.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I must've surprised you.
No, not at all.
I was just sort of
spacing out, I guess.
Please let Chi help!
Chi came here to work, Manager.
Oh, thank you very much, Chi.
Then you'd better
go into the other room
and get changed
as soon as possible.
Chi!
So uh, is something
wrong, Mr. Ueda?
Huh?
Well, I have to admit
you look a bit run down.
Chi?
Thanks.
But I'm fine, Motosuwa.
You know, I'm really
lucky to have Chi
to help out around here;
she's a very good worker.
Then, I guess everything's fine.
But listen.
If there is ever anything
you need help with,
you know where
to find me, right?
Motosuwa.
I was a total wreck
after Chi disappeared,
and you were there for me.
I felt so much better
after talking to you.
So, I'd like to do the same
if you need someone to talk to.
But don't take it the wrong way!
It's not just to pay
you back, of course.
I really appreciate it.
But I'm serious: there's nothing
the matter with me at all.
I just tend to be a
little awkward sometimes.
Huh?
I always want to see
a smile on the face
of the one I care about
the most in this world.
But somehow or other,
they always seem
to end up crying.
Mr. Ueda...
Chi changed!
Chi?
Ch-ch-ch-Chi , that outfit!
Um, Chi, that-that's
not the right one.
Huh?
This is wrong?
Yes Chi, I'm afraid
that's the wrong uniform;
that was made for someone else,
but I just couldn't bring
myself to get rid of it.
Huh?
Did Chi make a mistake?
Oh no, I'm the one
who made the mistake;
I should never have left it out.
I'm sorry about that, Chi.
Why don't you come with me, Chi,
I've got your uniform over here.
Yumi!
Huh?
I'm sorry, can you watch
Chi for me, please?!
Motosuwa, you shouldn't...
Yumi!
There's one thing I'm good at,
and it happens
to be running fast.
Y-Yumi?
So are Persocoms really
the best after all?
They're better than
real women, aren't they?!
Better than any woman, anywhere!
He told me he made
that outfit just for me.
But n-now a Persocom's...
Huh?
So does this mean the new dress
that Chi put on was actually
meant for you to wear?
Does it hurt?
Huh?
Do you hurt right here?
Is it an injury?
I'm not injured, Chi,
but thanks a lot.
But Chi doesn't understand.
Manager had a painful face.
It's still there.
Why does it always come to this?
I just made her cry again.
Not only that, I hesitated
when I should
have gone after her.
But Manager, it's different.
Yumi cried because
of Chi this time.
When she looked at Chi.
No, it's my fault.
Her goodbye was perfectly
clear last time.
Goodbye?
But no matter what I do,
somehow I just can't
seem to get over her.
Telephone!
Telephone! Telephone!
No answer.
Switching from telephone
to voice mail mode now!
Recording completed,
recording completed!
Hm...
May I help you?
Where's my applause?
Huh?
An ovation!
Sumomo has just done a fine job!
There should be applause!
Why do I even bother?
So what about my applause?
Yay! Woohoo!
Sumomo got applause!
I got applause!
What is it with
this place anyway?
All the Persocoms around here
are so strange, including Chi.
Hey! They're back!
Welcome back!
Is this person a guest of yours?
Yeah. So can you guys
keep it down for a while?
Aye!
Goodbye means, you can't
stay by their side anymore.
You won't see them anymore.
Goodbye is...
Goodbye is very hard.
Oh, Chi.
Manager feels the hurt
because of the goodbye.
So, was it Yumi who said
the goodbye to Manger?
Yes.
Does it hurt right
here no matter
who says the goodbye?
Do all goodbyes
feel the same way?
Well, it's true
that you feel lonely
whether you're the one
who says goodbye or they do.
But it's- it's the
goodbye that comes
from the one you
love the most...
that's the one that ends
up hurting you the most.
Well, you see,
I used to work at Tirol.
Mr. Ueda is a very nice person.
When he wasn't busy,
he'd even teach me
how to bake cakes
and cookies and things.
It's amazing what a sweet
and wonderful guy he can be.
He blushes easily,
and he's really cute too.
And so...
Well, I fell in love.
And one day, I summoned
up all my courage,
and asked him out.
I love you.
Uh, I uh, love you, too.
R-Really?
Y-Yes.
Really for real?
R-Really, for real.
I had that outfit made
just for you, Yumi.
Well, I thought it would be nice
if you could keep working here,
but, do you think
this is a good idea?
I mean, I'm a lot older
than you are, Yumi.
And, not only that,
but I was married before.
You were married?!
Yes, but my wife passed away.
Is that a problem for you?
N-No, that doesn't
matter one bit.
But, it sort of
stuck in my mind,
and I got curious
about what kind of person
he'd been married to.
So, without telling him,
I used a Persocom
and did a secret search.
Senpai, I was
wondering if you'd mind
doing a web search
for me right now.
Huh? Oh, no problem.
Can you do that, Sumomo?
Aye! Please give
me the keywords!
The terms I'd like you to look
for are "Hiryoyasu Ueda" "cake"
and "Tirol" and "marriage."
158 entries have been found.
How many of those are news
sites with video files?
There are two of them.
Um, I'd like to
show them on the TV.
Do you mind?
Uh, Sumomo!
Aye! To do that, please
connect me to the TV now.
Are you sure it
will actually work
with the connection
in a building like this?
Huh?
Do you really think it's
going to be a problem?
It takes an
exceptionally high bandwidth
to download video files in
any reasonable amount of time.
Therefore, it's
unadvisable to attempt to-
Huh?
Well that's a relief!
It looks like it's working.
Playing back the first file.
Did you have any
specific concerns
when you first decided
to marry a Persocom?
Oh, well I had some
reservations, or course.
For one thing, I was concerned
whether her marrying me
would really make
her happy or not.
But then, there all kinds
of different marriages
out there in the world,
and even though this one
may seem a little
unusual to some people,
I thought we'd be
able to build on
our happiness together and
it would develop over time.
Oh, I-I'm sorry!
I'm sure that must have
sounded very strange!
Playing back the second file.
Now that your marriage,
to a Persocom, has ended so
abruptly in a traffic accident,
how does that make you feel?
Is it true that the Persocom
protected you in the accident?
Would you ever consider
marrying another Persocom?
Do you plan to
cremate the Persocom?
Or are you just
gonna throw it out?
Mr. Ueda, apparently,
the Persocom
actually saved your
life, is that right?
She's not just a Persocom.
Please don't generalize and
diminish her life like that.
My wife had a proper name.
If you don't mind,
her name was "Yumi."
Huh?
Yumi?
I knew when I saw this,
that I would never be
able to measure up to her!
Yumi.
Yumi looked hurt too.
She had lots of water
coming from her eyes.
Water? You mean tears.
Why do tears fall out?
Tears flow from happy times
and from sad times.
So Yumi's tears were flowing
out because she is happy?
No, I'm sure those were
because she was sad.
She said that it
just made her sad
whenever I was around her.
There's really no
other way to explain it:
she must hate me, that's all.
What is hate?
It means that she doesn't
want to be together.
Why was Yumi out there,
looking inside the store?
She wants to be close
to someone she hates?
Well, not really...
Yumi is always looking
inside the store from outside.
Huh?
Over there; she was
always watching you,
and her face looked painful.
But she was different
a few minutes ago.
When Chi put on this outfit,
lots of tears came
from Yumi's eyes.
Right after she
saw these clothes.
That outfit is Yumi's.
Why does Yumi look
like she feels hurt
when she sees
this outfit on Chi?
Now Manager has a painful look.
Painful is very hard.
What would be best to do?
What does Manager want to do?
What do I want to do?
I guess I...
Chi, I need to ask
you a favor of you.
So when it hit me like that,
that I'd be somehow
be compared to her...
the idea was just too awful.
Because, well
Persocoms always do
everything so perfectly.
I thought it was
better to say goodbye
before I disappointed him.
But it's just no good.
It's even harder now than
it was before we broke up!
I understand.
It was tough for you, wasn't it?
Because by then you cared
about Mr. Ueda too much.
You're like a big brother.
So I'm like your big brother?
But anyway, I'm sure it was
just as tough on Mr. Ueda,
And even though his
first wife was a Persocom,
I'm sure it wasn't just
some decision he made lightly.
You're right. I know
that he wouldn't do that.
Yeah.
And if he was acting
that way towards you,
it can only mean
that you must've been
very special to him, Yumi.
What happened to
her was terrible,
and it must have been
the hardest time
in his whole life.
And yet, in spite of everything,
he was somehow able
to fall in love again.
I think that's just amazing.
So the truth is, I don't think
he'd ever compare you
with someone from his past.
But what about you?
Wouldn't it bother you
just a teeny bit, Senpai?
Me? Well,
I don't know.
Yeah, I guess I would.
But, I wouldn't make any
comparisons like that.
Why do you say that?
Because I think
I can imagine how
I'd feel if someone
did that to me.
He couldn't do something
like that anymore than I could.
He's not that type of person.
Thank you, Motosuwa.
Chi!
Manager!
But how did you
know we were here?
Well, actually; I got
a little help from Chi.
She did me a really big favor;
she was able to
locate Yumi by accessing
the number to
her mobile Persocom.
And here we are.
How could that be?
I don't get it; it never rang.
Huh?
I'm sorry to intrude
on you like this.
No, please come on in.
I'm sorry, this is all my fault.
No, you didn't do
anything, Manager.
That's easy to say,
but it's not true.
It is my fault; if I had
explained it to you properly,
I'd have spared you
every one of those tears.
The reason that
I decided to ask Yumi
to get married to me
in the first place was
because of who she was.
It wasn't just because
she was a Persocom.
And that's just how I felt
when I fell in
love with you, Yumi,
because of who you are.
Yumi, somehow you think that
that "Yumi," the
Persocom, was perfect.
But believe me;
it wasn't like that.
There are things
that they can do
because they're Persocoms,
but there're some
things they can't do
because they're Persocoms.
It's really just
the same as people
having certain things they
can or can't do, that's all.
I thought that I'd never
be able to fall in love again.
Especially that I'd
never be able to fall
in love with another Persocom.
But, you know,
even if you were
a Persocom, Yumi,
I think I would have fallen
in love with you anyway.
Oh, Yumi, I'm sorry!
What have I done?
I made you cry again!
Chi?
C-Chi?!
Chi made a mistake.
Here. Manager said that
this outfit belongs to Yumi.
Thank you.
Manager, I, um, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I was... I just...
Thank you for falling
in love with me!
Chi?
There are things
that they can do
because they're Persocoms,
but there're some
things they can't do
because they're Persocoms.
It's really just the
same as people having
certain things they can
or can't do, that's all.
Even if you were
a Persocom, Yumi,
I think I would have fallen
in love with you anyway.
Chi.
Hideki.
Happy holding hands?
Chi...
Ah, it looks like The One
Just for Me has been decided.
I guess I have no choice
but to go over there now.
I hope that this turns
out to be a happy ending.
Hm?
What's going on?
Nothing.
Hm?
One person completely
fills me up.
I'm happy when
that person laughs.
I'm happy when that
person is by my side.
Yes. I feel happy when
that person is happy.
Different from the others,
that person is my dearest...
my special one...
"The One Just for Me."
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Decides."