It's almost summer time.
This is going to
be my 18th summer.
But for a guy like me
who didn't get into college,
it doesn't matter
if it's summer or not.
Studies come first,
studies come second,
and that's pretty
much all there is.
Hmm.
Your grades don't seem
to show much improvement at all.
I-I'm sorry.
Oh, don't be so glum about it.
It's all right.
If you really apply
yourself this summer,
I'm sure you'll
be quite surprised
with the results by the
time fall rolls around.
Uh, do you really think so?
You'll be fine.
That's true, isn't it?
They say that summer's
when everything gets decided!
So I'll do the best I can!
That's right, Motosuwa,
do your best!
You bet I will!
Senpai!
Uh, Yumi, wha-
So tell me: what do
you think of my swimsuit?
I bought it just for today!
It, yeah, it looks great on you!
It really does.
Isn't it wonderful...
that it's so nice out today?
Oh, ah, Miss Shimizu...
Okay, we're ready.
I'm all done helping
Chi get dressed.
Miss Hibiya!
Chi.
Hideki!
Chi!
So then, maybe I really
am here at the beach.
Senpai!
Is it all right for me
to be here right now?
Since I just got a D on
the practice exam...
...and with no money
or time to spare...
That's right,
Motosuwa, do your best!
You bet!
Okay then, that's great.
See you at the
beach this weekend!
Huh?
The beach. It was Shinbo's idea.
You've heard about it, right?
Huh?
Three days and two nights?
That's right.
You wouldn't want
to miss a chance
to go to the beach, would you?
No, but why does it
have to be so long?
I don't have that
kind of money...
Okay, just hear me out.
You know Kokubunji.
He goes to his private beach
about this time every year.
We just happened to get a chance
to tag along with him this time.
So that means it's free.
It's free?
We can't do those
kind of things;
we're not college students yet.
There's no time to
run off to the beach.
Uh, Mr. Motosuwa?
Y-Yes?
I thought this might be
a good swimsuit for Chi,
if you need one.
It's one of my old ones,
and it should be fine.
Huh?
Yeah I invited our
landlord while I was at it.
And also what's-her-name, Yumi?
Everybody told me that
they're gonna be coming.
You sure you don't
want to come with us?
Oh dear, Mr. Motosuwa,
you're really not
that busy, are you?
Oh no, that's not what I...
it's nothing like that. I just-
Chi?
Just make it through the
summer, entrance exam loser.
Am I gonna be alright?
Motosuwa, this girl's
your Persocom, right?
Oh, uh, yeah.
Chi, I think it's time
you said hello to Yumi
and Miss Shimizu.
Good evening.
Oh no, so close.
It's afternoon now, right?
What's the greeting
for afternoon, Chi?
Chi?
Good afternoon.
Good afternoon to you.
That was perfect Chi;
I'm proud of you.
That's a cute
Persocom you've got.
It's nice to finally
get to meet you, Chi.
Chi.
Hey, Motosuwa!
Come on, hurry up and
get your swimsuit on!
Do you plan to
stand around all day?
We're gonna run out of
time to play you know;
you don't think
the sun's gonna wait.
Go get Mr. Motosuwa.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Chi?
One, two, three, four, two, two,
three, four, three,
two, three four.
Lots of water.
Yeah. This is called the ocean.
Ocean?
Right.
Ocean.
Okay, I know!
Is everybody ready to go
take a dip in the ocean?
Sure!
Oh, do be careful;
the water can get very deep
quite suddenly around here.
We will!
Wow, look at him;
he's just like a
great big puppy.
Well, it's a good
opportunity, I'd say.
Let's go have some fun.
It's so salty!
You got splashed
because you were
looking the other way!
Salty?
That's right.
It's not like regular water;
ocean water is real salty.
Salty water.
By the way,
I wonder if it's safe'
for Persocoms to be immersed
in sea water like this.
Chi?
Oh, you don't have
to worry about that;
Persocoms are
definitely waterproof
for everyday life.
Oh, I see, that's true.
So you're even a nice guy
to a Persocom,
aren't you, Senpai?
Huh?
Gotcha!
You little rat!
Take this! And that!
I'll getcha!
Hey, I know, why don't
we all swim over there?
Yeah, that sounds
great! Let's go!
I'm... well, I think
I'll pass on that.
I can't swim.
Oh please, come on.
No, I'm not kidding, it's true.
Well, I'm not gonna try
and force you or anything,
but, Motosuwa, I'm not
gonna let you go at night.
At night; why's that?
What's that supposed to mean?
We'll have a private lesson.
In my room tonight.
Be ready for it.
You bet I will!
Wow, for you to
have your own resort
at a place like this...
...you must really have quite
an amazing family, Minoru.
That's not necessarily true.
Well, after all, I mean,
this is what you call
a private beach, right?
Actually, not.
It's just that
nobody else is here
at the moment, that's all.
There.
I'm all done with the checkup.
Right.
Well, you know,
maybe we are getting in
your way a bit with all this?
What do you mean?
Well, you know:
a bunch of us being
so rowdy and all.
Well, it's true
that you're rowdy.
It really is quite lively
this year, Lord Minoru.
That's true.
Then again, it's rather nice
to have people around
every once in a while.
Oh, I see.
Hey!
You didn't come to the beach
to sit and read, did you?
Play time! Play time!
Shall we?
Here it comes!
Here we go! Try this one!
Here!
Here it comes, Chi!
Do your best!
A ball. Hideki gave me a ball.
Time to eat!
Mmm!
Chi.
All right! Here we go!
Here we go!
I guess this must be
what you call happiness.
Yeah, well you hafta admit
it did help clear your mind.
Yep.
But don't think for
a minute it means
that I've lost the will
to study or anything.
I said I'd spend
the summer studying,
and nothing can stop me!
Yeah, yeah.
I lose again!
Hey, why don't we play
a little poker next?
Let me think:
I'm pretty sure Miss Shimizu's
room was one of these,
but which one could it be?
Oh... This is it.
We'll have a private lesson
in my room tonight.
A lesson at night?
A special summer memory,
or something along those lines?
Yes?
Um, it's Motosuwa.
Oh, hi, the door's open.
Come on in.
O-Okay.
Something wrong?
Please, come in.
Hm?
Um, here I come.
Is everyone here now?
Huh?
Hey!
Hm?
Very good, then we
can start our class now.
Right.
Good morning!
Oh, so you finally got up?
You should use
some of this. Here.
What's this stuff?
Anti-oxidation cream;
you're supposed to use
it on your Persocom.
Huh?
Ocean breezes, seawater,
and sand are the sworn enemies
of delicate electronic
equipment like her.
I highly recommend it.
But wait, they're waterproof
for everyday life, right?
Yes, that's definitely true,
but you're still much better off
taking good care of them.
Besides, all you
have to do is to rub it
all over their bodies,
so it's really not that hard.
Oh, I see...
All over their bodies.
Chi?
You mean I do it?
I hafta rub it all over Chi?
Three... two... one.
Chi?
Ah! I can't!
There's just no way I can do it!
Yes, well, I suppose you could
teach her to do it herself.
Yeah!
Good idea!
Good morning, everybody!
Good morning, Yumi.
What's going on down there?
Let's see... All right, Chi.
First off, you squeeze out
a little cream like this...
Ah! No, don't do it like that.
Chi?
Mr. Motosuwa!
Would you like me to come down
and give you a hand with that?
Great! If you
wouldn't mind, that is.
Just wait here
for a minute, okay?
Splash splash,
splash splash. Whoa!
Splash splash.
Nice setup!
Chi!
Spike it!
Yeah!
Here!
Hideki, what is this?
Hm? What's what?
Oh, that's a seashell, Chi.
Seashell.
So, what's that?
Oh that? That's another shell.
Shell.
Is this, too?
That's right. Huh?
A walking shell?
N-No, it isn't, it's...
It's, um on the
tip of my tongue;
it's something like uh...
A hermit crab.
They're called hermit
crabs, Motosuwa.
Oh!, That's right!
Hermit crabs!, They're
called hermit crabs, Chi.
Hermit crabs.
So, have you been
teaching her new words?
As a matter of fact, yes.
There's so many
things she's never seen,
so I try to spend as much time
as I can explaining them to her.
Hideki, what's this?
Let's see, is it kelp?
Or "wakame"? Or "mozuku"?
Why not just say seaweed?
Good idea. Seaweed.
It's seaweed, Chi!
Seaweed, this is seaweed.
Chi.
So, what's that?
Hey, wait a second, Chi.
Hideki, what's that?
I'd be more than happy
to help, if you need any.
Uh, yes, please;
that'd be great.
I'm sleepy.
I think I'll take a nap.
Hideki...
Huh?
What's that?
They're dolphins!
Oh my gosh,
those are real dolphins!
Wow, Chi!
I'm so impressed that you
noticed them; that's great!
Chi?
Hey guys, look:
it's a whole buncha Dolphins!
Oh sure, you see
them around here
from time to time.
I had no idea.
That's really cool!
I've seen 'em on TV a few times,
but never anything like this!
They're beautiful, aren't they?
Wow, so does that mean
they live around here?
They're pretty far away,
but we saw 'em, didn't we?
They're really far out there.
I wish we could
get a closer look.
I wonder if they'll
get any closer than that?
Closer?
But they mustn't do that;
if they come into the bay,
I don't think they'll
be able to get back out.
I see what you mean.
Yeah, but you just don't
get a chance like
this every day.
I'd like to get closer too.
Mmm hmm.
Okay, then let's just
swim out to where they are.
They can't be that
far out, can they?
S-Senpai?
Yesterday, when you told us
that you didn't
know how to swim,
you really weren't kidding
about that, were you?
No, I wouldn't joke
about anything like that.
Yeah, but still,
you can do something really easy
like the breaststroke, right?
For real?
Yes, well don't let
that bother you;
everyone has their
strengths and weaknesses.
Yeah, that's right, Senpai!
There's a bright side,
just so you don't get depressed.
You'll be happy to
know there's no swimming
on the entrance exam.
Hideki cannot swim.
Is that amazing? Is he amazing?
Dolphins...
They're right in
front of my eyes.
Well, I guess I have no choice.
Amazing! His very
own personal boat.
Yep, it's something, all right.
You know, it's
starting to bug me.
Isn't it a little unfair
for one person
to have everything?
It doesn't seem right, does it?
Look at that!
This is the best place to be
if you want to go
dolphin watching.
Look at that!
Did you see that, Chi?
Hideki, is it fun to
watch dolphin splashing?
Of course it is!
Wow, cool!
Amazing!
Wow, look how awesome they are.
Splashing.
It's fun.
Chi will splash, too.
Miss Chi!
Chi?
Oh, no!
Chi!
What? Where'd she go?
Motosuwa, you gotta save her!
Huh?
But she's supposed
to be waterproof
enough for everyday life.
Idiot!
What's the matter with you?
This isn't "everyday life"!
This water's really deep!
Chi.
Motosuwa!
Senpai! I thought
you couldn't swim!
Where am I?
Kokubunji's resort house.
Geez, Senpai, don't go
doing things like that, okay?
That's right.
But it's so like you, Motosuwa,
to try to rescue her
without even thinking about it.
I-I'm sorry.
W-Where's Chi?
Hideki.
So then you're all right?
Chi is all right.
It looks like she didn't get
any water inside of her, either.
Is Hideki angry?
Did Chi do something bad?
I'm not angry.
I'm just glad you're all right.
Chi.
Hideki!
Boy, she certainly is
one peculiar Persocom.
Usually, when they're submerged
in the ocean,
water seeps in somehow,
and they get all messed up.
That's true.
You know, the truth is that
if Chi had been
a normal Persocom,
the outcome might've
been very different today.
Yes, that's true.
Huh?
What she's getting
at, Mr. Motosuwa,
is that Chi was the
one who saved you.
Huh?
I see. Well, thank you, Chi.
One, two, three, four,
two, two, three, four.
My summer is over.
Studies come first,
studies come second.
Summer's the crucial battle,
and I look forward
to better grades.
My grades are going down!
Hideki, is summer hot?
Boy is it ever.
Summer's really hot;
your brain gets fuzzy,
and it's hard to get motivated.
Summer means mosquito incense?
That's true.
The smell of that
incense burning
is the very smell of summer.
Miss Shimizu comes
in the summer?
That's right.
Nothing like Miss Shimizu
in the summer time.
Which means...
Huh?
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Entertains."
My pleasure!
My pleasure.