Narrator: Previously,
on "jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
♪
Jotaro: Hey, old man,
something’s off.
You’re going
the wrong direction.
Both: Hmm?
Jotaro: You seem to be
heading toward that island.
Joseph: But before
we arrive in Egypt,
we need to make a slight detour.
Someone is waiting for us
on the island.
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
- Polnareff: Hmm.
Joseph: He’s a man
who is extremely important
to our journey.
Polnareff: What is that
supposed to mean?
( Birds calling )
Polnareff: Hey,
what’s the big idea?
Does someone actually live here?
This is such
a tiny, little island,
it’s practically deserted.
Kakyoin: I would have to agree.
Mr. Joestar, are you sure
someone actually lives here?
Joseph: He’s been living
on this island by himself.
A man told me back in India, and
i’m sure I heard him correctly.
Kakyoin: Wait a sec.
When you say a man--
polnareff: What?
Mangos from India?
( Kakyoin sighs )
( Jojo gasps )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Jotaro: Hate to interrupt,
but I thought you should know
someone’s watching us
from the grass over there.
Polnareff: What?
- Hey!
- ( Joseph gasps )
( Kakyoin gasps )
From the back, he looks--
polnareff: You’re right.
I know that face.
Hold on! Just wait!
Man: Eat up now.
Are you hungry, Michael?
How about you, prince?
I mixed in
those shells you love,
so make sure you share
with the others, all right?
And there’s lots more
where this came from.
Make sure to get nice and fat
so you’ll be
a tasty chicken, Lionel.
Kakyoin: It’s not possible.
That man...
Polnareff: It can’t be. It’s--
Joseph: Hold it.
I’m gonna go and talk to him.
The rest of you
just wait here for now.
( Jojo grunts )
Pardon me.
My name is Joseph joestar.
My friends and I
are currently traveling
on an expedition to Egypt.
Man: Go away! I won’t hear it!
( Jojo gasps )
Polnareff: His voice
sounds like...
Man: I won’t say it again.
Don’t talk to me. Got it?
No one ever comes to see me
when they have
actual good news to report.
I only get visitors
when something bad happens!
- Just shut up!
- ( Polnareff gasps )
Man: Go away!
Kakyoin: Mr. Avdol!
Jotaro: Avdol, wait.
Man: I said go!
Both: Hold on!
That’s impossible!
Joseph: That wasn’t avdol.
It was his father.
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
- Polnareff: His father?
Joseph: He withdrew from society
and lives alone on this island.
I’m sorry that I wasn’t able
to tell you about this earlier,
but if it ever
became known to dio
that we stopped at this place,
avdol’s father
would be put in grave danger.
I would never forgive myself
if that happened.
But for now, my focus
has to be on telling him
what every parent fears most,
that his son is dead.
( Polnareff gasps )
Avdol: Polnareff!
♪
( No audible dialogue )
( Polnareff sobbing )
Joseph: Don’t let yourself
go there.
Avdol’s death
wasn’t your fault.
Polnareff: No,
it’s entirely my fault.
I’ll carry that burden
for as long as I live.
Kakyoin: Is it safe to assume
his father’s a stand user?
Joseph: Yeah, but I don’t know
what kind of stand it is
or what sort of power it wields.
Kakyoin: Judging by the way
his father reacted to us,
I doubt he’ll offer us much
in the way of assistance.
Joseph: You just leave
the talking to me, all right?
Hopefully my words
will be able to reach him.
♪
( Waves crashing )
Polnareff: All I ever wanted
was to avenge my sister’s death,
and I ended up
killing my friend.
There’s nothing I could possibly
do to make it up to his father.
I’m between a rock
and a hard place.
( Sighs )
Talk about depressing.
Hmm?
♪
Huh?
Hmm. This thing is pretty shiny.
I wonder if it drifted up
from some sunken ship.
Just look
at all these barnacles.
It’s definitely
made of metal, but...
( Gasps )
There’s some kind
of creepy face carved on it.
Despite that,
it looks pretty valuable.
Now, if I can scratch
off these barnacles,
we’ll really be in business.
( Gasps ) What the hell?!
( Yelling )
It’s gone.
What in the world
happened just now?
From the looks of it, the air
trapped inside just burst out,
and I was scared over nothing.
Whew.
Given that it’s not aladdin’s
magic lamp or anything,
I guess I can relax a little.
♪
- ( Gasps )
- Creature: You get three...
- ( Polnareff yelps )
- Creature: Three, I say!
Your wish is my command.
Three wishes for whatever
your heart desires.
( Polnareff gasps )
What sort of fresh hell is this?
Cameo: I am known as cameo.
Allow me to thank you
for freeing me from the lamp.
Tell me your three wishes
so that I might
Grant them for you.
Polnareff: Hold it,
you smoky freak!
Are you a new stand user?
Silver chariot!
♪
Damn it.
This guy’s not half bad.
What awesome power.
Listen, buddy.
Your strength tells me
that your user
is definitely nearby.
Now who is it?
Cameo: Would you like
the answer to that question
to be considered
as your first official wish?
It’s a little on
the boring side, if you ask me.
Polnareff: Don’t pull
that "genie in a bottle" crap
with me, fait chier.
But if you’re saying you
could make me a super-rich man
right this instant,
let’s see it.
Cameo: Is that your first wish?
Going once.
Polnareff: Go ahead,
and Grant it if you can,
but otherwise stop
jerking me around, damn it.
Cameo: Then consider
your wish granted.
Polnareff: Huh?
Cameo: Hail 2 u!
( Polnareff yells )
Huh?
( Gasps ) Huh?
I don’t understand a single
thing that just happened.
So that strange guy wasn’t
the enemy’s stand after all.
I thought he’d attack me,
but instead he told me
to make three wishes.
I don’t know
what’s going on here,
but I don’t trust that guy.
Someone shady
is on this island.
It’s probably a good idea
to tell Mr. Joestar
what happened here.
There might be a chance
it could have something to do
with avdol’s father.
- ( Jangling )
- Huh?
That’s weird.
What’s up with all
that loud clanging back there?
( Jangling continues )
Hmm?
( Gasps )
Whoa, is this for real?
But it can’t be.
( Gasps )
W-wait, this is gold
from the napoleonic era.
This isn’t a dream
or an illusion. Holy crap!
A treasure trove of gold.
I wouldn’t believe it
if it wasn’t right here.
I don’t get it! What is this?!
Are you mocking me
or something?!
No, that’s not it.
He can’t be mocking me.
When could he have buried
this gold here?
There’s no way
he would have had time
to Bury it
after I made my wish,
so how the hell
did that freak do all this?
Cameo: Now what is
your second wish?
Your wish is my command.
Polnareff: This doesn’t
make any sense!
Why are you doing this?!
What are you scheming?!
You don’t think i’d fall
for your stupid tricks?
If you are my enemy,
then fight me like one.
If not, i’ll take
this treasure for myself.
Cameo: So I take it knowing
the answer to that question
is your second wish?
Though, it’s a little on
the boring side, if you ask me,
but I owe you
a debt of gratitude
for letting me out of that lamp,
so I shall Grant your wish.
Polnareff: You know,
you’re a smug bastard.
All right, then.
Have it your way.
I do have a wish.
I want to be a comic artist!
That was always my dream
back when I was a kid.
And don’t make me
some pathetic one either.
I wanna be bigger than Disney.
In fact, someday i’m gonna
build my own polnareff-land!
You know what?
Scratch that idea.
Just give me a second to think.
Any minute now,
it’ll come to me.
I’ve made up my mind!
I want a beautiful girlfriend!
( Sighs )
More than money or fame,
what I want is true love.
I’m talkin’ not only
someone who’s really cute,
but a girl who will pinky swear
she loves me with all her heart.
I wanna meet a girl
who feels the same way about me
as I do for her.
So if that’s
within your power to do,
then prove it to me
right now, damn it!
Cameo: You want a girl, do you?
Very well.
Polnareff: Wait. No, never mind.
I need time
to think this through.
( Waves crashing )
( Gasping )
I have a question.
Do you have the ability
to revive someone?
Cameo: Am I to assume
your wanting to know the answer
to that question
is your second wi--
polnareff: Cut it out!
I’m asking you to bring
my dead sister back to life.
And while you’re at it,
you can do the same
for my friend avdol.
That shouldn’t be too much
of a challenge, right?!
♪
Cameo: Ah. Very well.
I shall Grant your wish.
( Polnareff gasps )
Wha--are you serious?
♪
Polnareff: So you
can really do it?
Cameo: Indeed, but know
that since you made two wishes,
i’ll Grant them
in the order you asked.
First I will Grant
your second wish,
to bring back your sister.
Hail 2 u!
Polnareff: Hey,
don’t just disappear!
Who the hell are you,
and why are even you doing this?
( Scraping )
( Gasps )
What was that sound?
I’m sure I heard
something rustling around.
It sounded like someone
was digging up the ground.
- ( Scraping )
- ( Gasps )
There’s that
weird digging again.
W-where’s that sound
coming from?
( Panting )
No. Impossible.
( Woman crying )
Polnareff: Wait.
Is that a woman crying?
All right,
who the hell’s back here?!
( Gasps )
T-these are...
( Woman crying )
♪
Polnareff: These are
strands of hair,
and a woman’s hair, no less.
A woman’s footsteps.
It can’t be!
( Crying resumes )
There’s no way.
This can’t be happening,
can it?
As far as I know,
my little sister is still
in her coffin back in France,
so how could she be--
just who the hell are you?!
You better answer me right now!
Woman: Please stay away.
( Polnareff gasps )
Woman: I’m in so much pain.
My body hasn’t fully formed yet.
Polnareff: I know that voice.
Sherry, it’s you.
( Waves crashing )
Joseph: Polnareff’s
been gone awhile.
Where’d he run off to?
Jotaro: I couldn’t
find him up top.
Kakyoin: Where could
he have gone?
It’s already nightfall,
and he’s nowhere to be seen.
Jotaro: Do you think that he
could have gotten tangled up
in a fight with the enemy?
Polnareff: Sh-Sherry...
Am I hallucinating,
or is it really you?
♪
It is you, isn’t it?
( Gasps )
( Birds chirping )
- Huh?
- ( Rustling )
Wait! Where are you going?
Where are you going, Sherry?!
Wait, Sherry. It’s only me.
Sherry, why are you
running away?
Where are you?!
Come on, Sherry, please!
I’m begging you
to show yourself!
Let me see your face.
Let me see it one more time.
( Sherry laughs ) Hey, brother!
( Laughs )
Higher, brother!
Raise me as high as you can!
Yay! Now spin me around!
( Laughing )
Oh, it’s simply wonderful.
I’ve been wanting
a new umbrella.
Thank you for buying it for me.
I’m off now.
♪
Polnareff: Sherry!
Sherry!
( Gasps )
mon dieu,
what the hell happened here?
They’ve been half eaten.
( Gasps )
Sherry!
Can you hear me?
Why are you running away?!
It’s me, your big brother!
Sherry: Because my body
is covered in mud.
( Sobbing )
And there’s my hair.
It’s so unkempt.
Polnareff: It’s okay, Sherry.
Don’t worry about that.
You’ve gotta believe me when I
say you’re perfect as you are.
( Sherry crying )
Polnareff: Why are you crying?
Sherry, talk to me.
Why are you sad?
♪
Oh...
Oh, Sherry.
- Sherry: No.
- Polnareff: Eh?
Sherry: Just stay back.
Don’t come any closer.
Polnareff:
W-what are you saying?
You’re not making any sense.
Sherry: It’s simple.
I’m saying you’ll hate me.
Polnareff: Oh, Sherry,
have I ever said anything
to make you think i’d hate you?
Sherry: Yes, you have.
It was when we were
little kids and I gave
your favorite tropical fish
to that stupid cat.
You got really angry over it
and said you hated me.
Polnareff: I admit
I was angry that day,
but no matter what,
i’ve always loved you
more than the stars in the sky,
and I still do.
Sherry: Really?
You’ve always loved me,
no matter what I did?
Polnareff:
Yes, of course I have.
Sherry: And does that feeling
hold true to this day?
Polnareff: I will always
love you, no matter what,
and I can clearly see now
that you’re the real Sherry.
You have no idea how much
i’ve missed you, little sister.
Sherry: I see.
I feel the same, big brother.
Polnareff: Sherry,
please look this way.
I’m begging you to show me
that beautiful face of yours.
( Sherry crying )
Polnareff:
Why are you crying, Sherry?
Are you still sad?
Sherry: Sad? No, brother.
These aren’t tears of sadness.
I’m crying, because...
Polnareff: What?
What is it, then?
Sherry: I’m--
i’m happy, brother,
’cause I can finally eat you!
( Polnareff screaming )
Ch-chariot.
( Gagging )
Sher...ry.
Sherry: I’m sorry
that I bit you, brother.
I’m afraid my body is
still underdeveloped.
But if I eat your flesh,
i’ll return to normal.
It’s okay if I eat you, right?
What am I saying?
You always did
what I asked you to.
( Growling )
( Polnareff screams )
Cameo!
Cameo: You rang?
Polnareff: You bastard!
Cameo: What’s all
the fuss about?
Do you have a complaint?
I granted your wish, didn’t I?
Granting wishes
is my power, after all.
What you do with them
is completely up to you.
( Polnareff gasps )
Then let me
use this opportunity
to tell you my third wish.
Ma-make my sister...
♪
Make her...
Make my sister
return to her grave
so she can rest in peace!
Cameo: I don’t think so.
( Polnareff gasps ) Why not?
Cameo: You still don’t get it
do you, polnareff?
If you haven’t figured it out,
i’m a stand
and not just any stand,
the one represented
by the judgment card.
You see, my powers allow me
to extract wishes
from the deepest corners
of the human mind
and manifest it
from the soil below.
You created your sister
from your own yearning.
Polnareff: How dare you?
Cameo: And since you
created her, I cannot undo it.
( Laughs )
It looks like the winner
of this battle is me.
( Polnareff gasping )
Cameo: By the way,
I seem to recall
you saying something
about a third wish.
But don’t you remember,
polnareff?
You’ve already made
your third wish.
Polnareff: Oh, no.
( Cameo laughs )
Polnareff: You don’t mean him.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian