narrator: Previously
on "jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
- Man: ...Ka...
- Announcer: ...Kyo...
- Man #2: In...
- Cartoon: Beware...
- Man #2: Of...
- Woman: Him.
- Man #3: Di...
- Woman #2: O’s...
- Woman #3: Loy...
- Man #1: ...Al...
Cartoon: Servant!
Joseph: Dio!
So then, where is kakyoin?
Avdol: He’s with jotaro.
♪
Girl: Oh!
Can I get some ice cream,
please?
Vendor: Welcome.
You know,
ice cream is pretty good,
but this baby here,
chilled coconut juice,
nothing in the world like it.
How ’bout it?
Girl: Uh...
Jotaro: I guess we can try it.
Three, then.
Vendor: Thank you much.
That’s $12.
Girl: Hey, jerk!
What are trying to pull?
Make it six!
Kakyoin: Here.
This should cover it.
Vendor: Okay, thanks.
Enjoy!
Thief: Hah! I’ll take that!
( Laughs )
( Kakyoin grunts )
( Thief laughing )
( Yelps )
( Gasps )
♪
So you dumb, useless,
disgusting piece of shit,
who the hell
do you think you are?
- Girl: Eh?
- Jotaro: Huh?
Kakyoin: I’ll make you wish
you were never born!
Jotaro: Kakyoin!
Kakyoin: Get up,
you vile little cockroach dick.
Do I look like
easy pickings to you?
And now you’ll feel the pain!
How dare you touch my wallet
with the same grimy fingers
that wipe your filthy ass!
I can’t let you get away with
something like that, now, can I?
- ( Thief gagging )
- Kakyoin: Can I?
Come on! Tell me! Can I?!
- Can I? Can I? Can I...
- Jotaro: Kakyoin!
What are you doing to this guy?
You’ll kill the bastard.
Girl: How the...
Oh, my god, a back-breaker?
What a brutal move!
Kakyoin: Come on! Come on...
Girl: And he’s using
such filthy language.
It’s not like him at all.
Kakyoin: Come on.
Come on. Tell me.
Come on!
Jotaro: Kakyoin!
Now cut it out, damn it.
You’re losing control.
You’re acting
like such a bastard.
Something’s not right.
What the hell’s
gotten into you?
Kakyoin: That hurt, you know.
You didn’t
have to shove me around,
like you’re the one in charge.
That man tried
to steal my wallet.
He was committing a crime,
and criminals
should be punished.
Tell me, am I wrong, jotaro?
You’d do the same, old pal.
( Slurping )
Jotaro: This guy.
( Kakyoin slurps )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
What are you glaring at?
You know, the look in your eyes
is awfully hostile, jotaro.
What’s wrong?
Why are you so upset?
You couldn’t
possibly be thinking
about ending our friendship
over a little tussle
with a thief, now, would you?
You’re acting as if i’ve done
something unforgiveable.
- ( Girl gasps )
- ( Thief gagging )
Girl #2: Look, a beetle.
- Boy: That’s awesome!
- Boy #2: Where is it? Huh?
- Boy #1: Oh, wow!
- Boy #2: I see ’em!
Boy #3: There’s four
of ’em up there.
Boy #1: So cool! ( Laughs )
Kakyoin: Hmm?
( Laughs )
- Girl: Huh?
- Kakyoin: Jojo...
You’re making way too big
of a deal out of this.
I’m just having a bad day.
No big thing.
I’m so exhausted from the trip.
It’s put me in such a bad mood.
Jotaro: Just a bad mood, huh?
Seemed to me
you felt pretty good.
♪
The old man and avdol
think it’s a good idea for us
to head to India by train.
We leave tomorrow.
We’ll take the cable car
to Singapore station
to reserve tickets.
( Children chattering,
laughing )
Kakyoin: Hmm?
Girl: Mr. Kakyoin,
jojo’s left already.
Shouldn’t we get going?
- ( Kakyoin slurping )
- Girl: Huh?
Kakyoin: Ah, right.
I’ll catch up
in just a second.
Girl: Oh, okay.
I guess you must like
coconut juice a whole lot, huh?
( Kakyoin crunching )
♪
( Girl gasps )
( Kakyoin slurps )
( Crunches )
( Swallows )
( Girl gasps )
( Kakyoin spits )
Girl: Was that a b-beetle?
N-no, no.
I must be seeing things.
It must have been a piece
of coconut or something.
Kakyoin: Oh, yes,
I do love coconuts.
They’re my favorite.
( Girl shuddering )
Jotaro: What’s up, half pint?
Girl: Uh, nothing. Don’t worry.
( Jotaro sighs )
Kakyoin: Hey, jotaro.
Are you gonna eat that cherry?
If not,
then hand it over already.
I’m starving.
Uh-oh!
Better watch out, jotaro!
- ( Jotaro grunts )
- ( Girl screams )
Jojo!
( Kakyoin laughs )
Good one, huh? ( Laughs )
I’m only playing with you,
good ol’ jotaro.
Lick, lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick...
( Babbling )
Girl: It’s like he’s
a totally different person.
Kakyoin: That look again!
What’s with all this hardcore
glaring, jotaro, old pal?
Have you lost
your sense of humor?
♪
( Creak )
Jotaro: Get in, kakyoin.
The cable car just got here.
Now, I told you to get in.
See? I’ve got
your ticket right here.
I’m gonna knock
your crooked, possessed ass
right into that cable car.
Kakyoin: Huh? ( Groans )
- Jotaro: What the?!
- ( Girl screams )
( Kakyoin laughs )
You’re a bit off.
"Possessed"
isn’t quite the word.
Wanna give it another try?
Lick, lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick.
Jotaro: Wait a minute.
This isn’t kakyoin.
Imposter: Congrats on
not being as stupid as you look.
Though, you still
haven’t realized
my body’s been growing
this whole time, have you?
Jotaro: All right, who are you?
Is he a stand? Can’t be.
I was able
to touch him just now.
Unless he’s a stand
I can strike with my own fists?
Girl: Huh? Jojo!
Imposter: I can merge with
any organic matter I consume.
I’m a stand
anyone can see and touch.
Lucky them, don’t you think?
I’m yellow temperance,
of the temperance card.
Gaze upon my handsome face
with envy!
Come now, jotaro, old pal.
Take a good look at your hand.
See that little bit of me?
It latched on when you hit me
and really
doesn’t want to let go.
I advise you not to touch,
or it’ll go after
your left hand, too.
You should save your left hand
for picking your nose.
This stand is a slow eater,
and the more it eats,
the bigger it gets.
You’ll never get it off.
Jotaro: Crap!
Damn you.
Ora!
Temperance:
What do you mean, "ora"?
When I digest you,
i’ll shove your own crap
down your measly throat!
Jotaro: Enh! The hell?
This stuff burns.
( Temperance laughs )
( Jotaro gasps )
Damn bastard.
( Telephone line rings )
( Line picks up )
Girl: Hey, is this
Mr. Jojo’s grandpa?
He needs your help!
Joseph: Anne?
Tell me what’s wrong.
Anne: It’s Mr. Kakyoin!
Joseph: What about kakyoin?
Avdol: It’s true.
Seems he has betrayed us.
Anne: Mr. Kakyoin’s face split,
and now he’s a giant!
But Mr. Kakyoin wasn’t
Mr. Kakyoin. He’s a fake,
and jojo got attacked by some
weird slime on the cable car,
and now it’s eating his finger!
Joseph: Calm down, Anne.
Where are you now?
Anne: I’m at the cable car
station at the train center!
He’s being attacked!
Mr. Kakyoin went crazy
and is attacking jojo!
Joseph: Hurry, and come back
to the hotel as fast as you--
kakyoin: Did someone
say my name just now?
Avdol: Hmm?
Joseph: Where the hell
have you been?
Kakyoin: Hmm?
Jojo left me behind,
so I was sunbathing by the pool.
Avdol: With your
school uniform on?
Kakyoin: Yes. Why not?
Joseph: It’s all right.
We have the real one
here with us.
Anne, be careful. This means
your kakyoin is a fake!
Anne: I told you that!
( Screams ) Oh, no!
Jojo just jumped
out of the cable car!
♪
( Jotaro sighs )
Good freakin’ grief.
A stand that fuses with flesh?
It’s devouring my finger.
This could get bad.
First, i’ve gotta
get this stuff off me.
Might be easier said than done.
It might mean
I have to cut off my finger.
Temperance: Ha! Do you
really think you got away?
Sorry to burst your bubble,
ol’ pal.
Now dig that earwax
out of your ears,
and listen up, hotshot.
Your time’s run out,
’cause yellow temperance
has no weaknesses!
You didn’t escape!
It’s just that I
don’t have to chase you.
You’re as good as dead!
( Laughs )
Jotaro: This’ll hurt
like a son of a bitch,
but I don’t have a choice.
( Wincing )
Wait. What the hell?
The flame only made it
grow bigger.
That was a bad idea.
Damn. I thought I had it.
Hmm?
( Sighs )
( Star platinum grunts )
( Dog barking )
Jotaro: Pardon me.
Woman: My goodness. That’s
certainly a bizarre entrance.
Jotaro: Don’t mind me.
Hey, there, kid.
I’m gonna need to borrow
your popsicle for just a second.
( Boy gasps )
Woman: Hold on, young man.
What is it you think
you’re doing with that child?
- Jotaro: Is this your kid?
- Woman: No, he’s not, but--
jotaro: Then shut up, lady,
and enjoy the scenery.
Sorry, kid.
When we get down to the bottom,
i’ll buy you a new one, okay,
whatever kind you want.
Boy: Uh-huh.
If I can’t burn it off...
( Groans ) That bastard.
What? Now it’s forming needles
and digging even deeper
into my hand!
Woman: You really are stupid.
Nothing will work on it,
not even fire and ice.
( Jotaro gasps )
( Woman blows nose )
( Sighs )
I told you before, didn’t I?
You won’t find
a single weakness.
( Laughs )
( Dog whimpering )
Temperance: And now you’re mine,
you little shit!
( Laughs )
Jotaro: You’re the...
Boy: Papa! The puppy!
It’s got our puppy!
Jotaro: You bastard, you were
already in this cable car
waiting for me, weren’t you?
( Both yell )
Man: No!
Please don’t hurt pocky!
Jotaro: Watch out!
Don’t pull him!
Let go!
( Man screams )
Temperance: And now
it’s your turn to die,
jotaro, old pal!
Star platinum: Ora!
Temperance: Eh, you’re fast,
but...
I keep telling you
I don’t have any weaknesses.
Are you even listening to me?
You dumbass redneck!
My stand is armor
that can also absorb power,
a defensive wall
that can also attack.
No matter how fast you are,
no matter how strong or smart
you think you are,
against yellow temperance,
you are helpless!
There’s no way
you can defeat me.
You won’t survive,
unless, of course,
you suck it up and take
a cleaver to your right hand!
Do you understand?!
- ( Boy yells )
- ( Jotaro grunts )
Temperance:
Try as hard as you want,
but you have no way of winning!
You’re not getting out of this,
not until you’re digested.
I’ll eat you up!
Jotaro: Oh, good grief.
Temperance: Eh?
Jotaro: You’re right,
you really don’t have
any weaknesses.
Maybe you are
the world’s strongest,
and that’s terrifying,
but i’ll tell you, we kujos--
no, wait. I mean joestars.
We use strategy to fight
our way past any obstacle.
You haven’t won yet, and I
still have one strategy left.
Temperance: Really?
Jotaro: And that’s to...
Joseph: And that’s to...
Jotaro: Run away!
Temperance: What the hell?!
You’re in the middle
of being eaten alive,
you dumb-ass! My stand’s got
a hold that you can’t escape,
and you say you’ll run away?
Don’t make me laugh.
Jotaro: When I said run away...
I meant into the water.
Temperance: Damn it!
I--i can’t breathe.
( Gasps )
Jotaro: You let your stand’s
guard down to take a breath.
Your stand may be invincible,
but you sure as hell aren’t.
If I destroy you,
then your stand dies, too.
( Temperance gasps )
Jotaro: Do you understand?
Listen,
i’ve had it up to here
with that cocky-ass mouth
of yours, all right?!
I just happen
to be the type of guy
who takes these things to heart.
Ora!
( Temperance gags )
No, please, stop it.
I can’t fight anymore.
I’m through!
My beautiful nose
is completely shattered,
and my face is so messed up,
they’re gonna have to wire
my jaw shut, too. It hurts!
Spare me!
Dio, h-he paid me to do this.
( Coughs )
Look, I don’t plan
on risking my life
going after you guys.
There! See?
Jotaro: I want
something from you.
Temperance: Eh?
Jotaro: The other stand users,
I want all the info you’ve got.
Temperance: But that’s
the one thing I can’t say.
Don’t ask me that! Please!
I won’t do it!
I mean, I do have some pride,
you know.
I just can’t, okay?
Jotaro: Well, okay, then.
That’s honorable.
Temperance: I remember now!
There are four of them, okay?
One is the emperor,
then hanged man and empress,
and the last one goes by death.
Jotaro: Got it.
And what about their powers?
Temperance: Sorry.
I-I don’t know.
No, no, really!
I honestly don’t know any more!
Don’t you see? Stand users
don’t reveal their powers.
If they did, they’d be exposing
their weaknesses outright.
But I do know something.
Some witch
taught dio about stands,
and her son is one
of the four coming after you.
His name is centerfold.
He’s unmistakable,
because he has two right hands.
His card is the hanged man.
He’s the one who killed
polnareff’s little sister,
isn’t he?
I’ve heard the occasional rumor
about his powers.
A mirror.
Apparently, he uses a mirror.
I haven’t actually seen it,
but polnareff
has no chance of winning.
He’s dead meat.
- ( Water gurgling )
- Hmm?
( Chuckles )
I just noticed something,
jotaro.
( Laughs )
Looks like i’ve still got
some luck on my side.
Ha ha! Sucks to be you.
See that drain over there
off to your right,
the one with all
the blue crawdads?
Take a real good look.
Jotaro: Huh?
( Temperance laughs )
( Jotaro gasps )
A manhole.
( Temperance laughs )
That drainpipe
connects to this manhole!
It’s a perfect setup
for yellow temperance’s power!
I’m gonna pull you in
and hold you there!
Now you can’t attack me, loser.
I guess what I told you
about the man with two
right hands will go to waste.
You’re not gonna be able
to help poor polnareff,
jotaro kujo!
Aren’t I lucky to have
this drain to slurp you into?
And you thought you had me,
didn’t you?
Man, am I lucky!
Time to power up
with some crustaceans!
This is gonna be fun!
I’ll mash you up
and turn you into jelly,
and when I kill you, dio’s
gonna give me $100 million.
Ha ha!
A few minutes
of brawling with you,
and I will be set for life!
Aren’t I lucky?
Tell me i’m lucky,
you ball-less little butt-munch!
Jotaro: Good grief, really?
When you’re focused
on everything else,
it’s hard to observe yourself.
You don’t get it, do you?
Fine. Then i’ll
just beat the lesson in.
Your luck finally ran out.
Before, you got away
with only a broken nose.
Temperance: Huh?
Jotaro: When i’m done,
you won’t have
any bones left to break!
( Temperance yelps )
What did he just do?!
He punched me with water?!
( Screams )
♪
( Gasps )
( Shudders )
( Whimpers )
( Laughs )
I was only kidding around,
Mr. Jotaro.
I swear I was
just messing with ya, buddy!
Didn’t mean
anything by it, okay?
Be cool, man. Be cool.
It was just a prank!
Wait. Hang on a second.
You’re not thinking about
punching me any more, are you?
I’m seriously injured here.
My nose is badly broken,
and my jaw’s gonna
have to be wired shut.
( Laughs )
Jotaro: Just shut up already.
I have nothing more
to say to you.
You’re way too pathetic.
I’m done wasting my breath.
( Star platinum yelling )
Polnareff: Good grief.
So we’re
finally heading to India.
( Sighs )
And the man
with the two right hands
is called centerfold, right?
By the way,
where did Anne run off to?
Joseph: She was hanging around
Singapore station
right before
our train departed, but...
Avdol: She vanished.
Remember, she came
to Singapore to meet her father.
I’m sure she found him.
Polnareff: Yeah,
well, that story
about her meeting up with
her dad sounded fishy to me.
I bet she’s a runaway.
But it is a bit lonely without
that little rugrat, right, jojo?
( Jojo chuckles )
Kakyoin: But that stand
earlier was pretty creepy.
It freaks me out that a stand
could disguise himself as me.
Jotaro: You know,
i’ve been thinking about it.
He must have transformed
when I left the hotel.
Kakyoin: Jojo, those cherries,
are you gonna eat ’em?
Not to be greedy,
but they are my favorite.
Could I have one?
Jotaro: Yeah, sure.
Kakyoin: You’re the best.
Lick, lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick.
Lick, lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick, lick, lick.
Hey, look, jojo.
Flamingos in flight.
♪
Jotaro: Oh, good grief.
( Anne muttering )
( Snoring )
Jojo.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian