Avdol: You know your way
around a sword.
I’ll Grant you that much,
but it will take
much more than mere ego
if you think i’ll be defeated
by the time
the flames reach 12:00.
Your pride may well
be your undoing, Mr...
Uh, who...
User: Pardonnez-moi.
We haven’t been introduced yet.
My name is
Jean Pierre polnareff.
Avdol: Well met, polnareff.
It’s good to know the name
of one’s opponent.
However...
( All gasp )
Avdol: Back to the task at hand.
If you’re under the assumption
that my flames only burn upward
or with the wind
as they would in nature,
let me assure you they do not.
My stand is named
magician’s red,
because it wields fire
as though by magic.
( Polnareff scoffs )
Fire is what began life itself
in this world.
I should have expected as much
from a fiery stand
such as magician’s red,
who represents beginnings.
However, you dare to speak
of pride and ego?
I assure you that my pride
is well deserved!
♪
Joseph: In the fraction
of a second
that the coins lined up,
he skewered all five of them
in a single shot.
- Jotaro: No.
- Joseph: Eh?
Jotaro: Why don’t you
take a look at ’em again.
Kakyoin: It can’t be.
Avdol: There,
stuck on the blade of his sword.
He’s cut a bit of flame
for every coin that he hit.
Polnareff: Now you see
that i’m every bit as deadly
as I had said.
This is not mere ego.
My stand has the unrestricted
power to cut fire to ribbons,
as though it were nothing. Hmph.
It can slice through air,
creating a vacuum
and guiding the fire.
Your flames are useless.
Face it. Your magician’s red
may be fearsome,
but it’s powerless against
the likes of my silver chariot.
- ( Wood rattles )
- Avdol: Hmm?
How the devil...
Polnareff: Victory and conquest,
that represents
the card the chariot,
and defines my stand as well.
I can beat you
in this cramped little place
as well as anywhere else.
Not very sporting, though.
Your flames will serve you
to greater effect
in a larger, open space.
Beating you at the apex
of your powers, monsieur,
is the only victory
worthy of my stand.
All of you, follow me outside!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Joseph: What the hell
kind of nonsense is this?
( Polnareff laughs )
Kakyoin: I believe
they call it tiger balm garden.
Joseph: Oh, yeah?
Narrator: Tiger balm garden,
a fantastical hillside park
built along Hong kong’s
famous tai hang road.
With its surreal landscape
of sculptures and pagodas,
it is a true Hong Kong oddity.
Polnareff: A prediction,
if I may indulge.
Monsieur avdol,
you will die here,
destroyed by the flames of your
very own stand, magician’s red.
- ( Avdol growls )
- Jotaro: Avdol.
Avdol: Jotaro,
this is not your fight.
In an open space like this one,
there’s nothing to keep my stand
from fighting at full force.
( Yells )
( Magician’s red squawks )
♪
Polnareff: En garde!
( Chuckles ) Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come, now. Nothing at all?
No sign of the flame
you were crowing about before?!
Suit yourself!
I shall press the attack!
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on!
( Avdol yells )
( All gasp )
Joseph: That goddamn bastard,
he’s just toying with us.
He used magician’s red’s
own fireballs
to make a statue of it.
Polnareff: Look at that.
( Chuckles )
In a place this odd,
I dare say your fiendish face
is right at home.
( Avdol growls )
( Chorus singing
in foreign language )
Polnareff: Well, here it comes.
Show me your true power
at last, avdol,
but know that it
will never be enough.
Joseph: Hey,
hide behind something already.
Avdol’s gonna blow his top!
Jotaro: What are
you talking about?
Avdol: Crossfire...
Hurricane!
( Magician’s red shrieks )
Polnareff: Really, is that
the best that you’ve got?
I told you before
what my sword does.
It creates a gap
between the pockets of air
so I can slice your flames!
( All gasp )
( Magician’s red shrieks )
Joseph: Avdol, no!
The fire is so intense,
it’s burning
stand and user alike!
( Avdol groaning )
( Polnareff laughs )
It’s just as I foretold.
You will die from an inferno
of your own making.
( Avdol grunts )
( Magician’s red squawks )
Polnareff: Good grief,
just die already.
One last pathetic gasp?
This is hard to watch!
( Gasps ) That hit felt wrong.
What is this?
What?
Impossible.
How can his stand injure me
after the moment
of its own destruction?
Joseph: It’s not the stand,
you bastard!
It’s a dummy!
Avdol: The flames
blinded your eyes.
What you really destroyed
was the statue that
silver chariot carved earlier.
Perhaps you didn’t
take me at my word
when I told you that I could
control my flames freely.
When you deflected it,
I used it to melt
the statue’s joints
and allow it to move.
The one defeated
by his own stand’s powers
is you, polnareff!
Now let’s try this again.
Crossfire hurricane!
( Polnareff screams )
Avdol: Challenging
a fortuneteller
in a battle of predictions
is a bold move.
Give it another decade,
and you would have been
a viable opponent.
Joseph: Such terrifying power.
His stand must have melted
in the face of such an attack.
It’s done for.
Jotaro: That’s one hell
of a burn.
I’m betting he’s dead
or wishes he was.
Yeah.
He’s not getting up from that.
Kakyoin: If he is alive,
he’ll be flat on his back
for months.
Having your stand destroyed
is a major trauma.
Avdol: Now then, Mr. Joestar,
let us resume our trek to Egypt.
Joseph: Mm.
( Avdol gasps )
Joseph:
What the hell’s going on?
His stand just exploded
into a bunch of pieces.
Kakyoin: How is he
still lying down,
but suspended in midair?
Polnareff: Bravo!
Well done, monsieur. Bravo.
- Joseph: That’s impossible.
- Avdol: I don’t believe it.
Kakyoin: He doesn’t
look injured at all.
Jotaro: Yeah, but...
Why the hell’s
he floating in the air?
( Polnareff chuckles )
Look with your inner eye,
and see the truth.
( Avdol gasps ) How can it be?
♪
Polnareff: Mais oui, messieurs.
He may have shed his armor,
but it’s still
my silver chariot.
You seem
quite taken aback by this.
I really should explain
before I destroy you.
Otherwise it wouldn’t
be chivalrous. Don’t you agree?
I’m sure you were
expecting nothing less.
If you don’t mind,
may we take a short timeout
for an explanation?
( Avdol groans )
Very well.
Let’s hear this explanation.
Polnareff: First,
the explosion you saw
was not my stand
self-destructing.
What you took as
silver chariot’s body was armor,
armor that was cast off.
But before it did, it absorbed
the brunt of your flames.
That’s how
I escaped further harm.
And bereft of armor, it has
significantly more agility.
Were you able to see my stand
as it held me up?
That’s right. Silver chariot
can now move faster than before.
Avdol: Hmm. Illuminating.
You’re suggesting
it only stood there
and took
my crossfire hurricane head-on,
because the armor didn’t
allow it to dodge. Is that it?
But, bereft of armor,
it is also far more vulnerable.
It may have survived
my attack once before,
but if it were hit again,
its destruction
would be absolute.
Polnareff: Hmph. That may be.
Oui. How can one know?
Such a shame
we’ll never find out.
Avdol: Never, huh?
Mind if I try it out?
Polnareff: First, let me
show you all something
that will
really freak you out.
Avdol: Well? Go ahead, then.
Joseph: What the devil?
He now has six--
no. No, wait. He has
a total of seven stands now.
Kakyoin: But that’s impossible.
There should only be
one stand per user.
( Avdol gasps )
Polnareff: Tell me,
are you freaked out yet?
These are after-images.
( Laughs )
Perfect mirrors
of the silver chariot,
guaranteed to fool your senses.
Your sight, your hearing,
your senses can’t follow
their movement.
How do you like its
swordsmanship now, monsieur?!
♪
( Avdol grunts )
Suffer my red bind!
( Magician’s red squawks )
( Polnareff laughs )
I told you that efforts to track
it would be in vain, did I not?
You waste your flame on images
and spare the real threat.
( Avdol roars )
( Magician’s red squawks )
Polnareff: Striking at random.
Desperation is not a good look
on you, my dear avdol.
He’s going
to exhaust himself at this rate.
Avdol: Crossfire...
Hurricane!
Polnareff: Mais non.
Mais non. Mais non. Mais non.
Have you learned nothing
at all today?
You’re a fool whose attacks
will not work on my stand!
Now give up!
Come on. Come on. Come on!
Jotaro: Avdol.
Avdol: What precision.
What lethal efficiency.
It’s plain to see.
His stand’s ability has been
trained and at great length.
Polnareff: Hmm. I’ve spent
the last decade honing my skill.
You had better hit me
with everything you’ve got,
for I intend my next attack
to be the coup de grace.
Avdol: It’s very
chivalrous of you
to keep giving me fair warning
about your next move.
Your honor is unimpeachable.
You’ve inspired me.
Thus, I, too,
will give fair warning
before my next attack.
( Polnareff scoffs ) Really?
Avdol: My crossfire hurricane
comes in more varieties
than the one
you’ve already seen.
It’s a flame
in the shape of an ankh,
but it need not remain whole.
I can divide it into
as many pieces as I deem fit.
Crossfire hurricane special!
( Magician’s red squawks )
Avdol: Try and dodge them!
Polnareff: You’re a fool, avdol!
It’s useless!
( Yells )
Joseph: Damn.
They’ve got him covered.
Kakyoin: He’s thought
of everything.
Polnareff: Naive, naive, naive!
So very naive!
I will wield
this divided flame against you
precisely as I did before.
Slice it, and hurl it back!
What?!
( Screams )
( Avdol sighs )
Joseph: That’s--that’s the hole
that was dug
by the flames earlier.
Now I get it.
It’s clear to me.
The first shot was a setup
and nothing more.
Then he used the tunnel to hit
him with crossfire hurricane.
Avdol: Like I said,
that attack can be divided up
into as many pieces
as are called for.
( Polnareff gasping )
Avdol: Burning is a painful way
to meet one’s end.
Take the knife,
and end it while you can.
♪
( Polnareff sighs )
My conceit was my undoing.
I couldn’t picture his fire
standing a chance
against my sword-work.
( Sighs )
A slow death amid the flames
is no less than I deserve,
monsieur.
I challenged you to this duel,
and you were the clear Victor.
I would not Sully it
with suicide.
It would be cowardly...
To end it myself.
( Avdol gasps )
Kakyoin: Hmph.
Avdol: Even in your
final moments,
you conduct yourself
with chivalry.
How easy it would have been
for you to throw that knife
into my unsuspecting back.
Even while working
for a devil like dio,
you’ve carried yourself
with honor.
Your death would be a waste.
Hmm?
Something must have set him
down this dark path.
Jojo.
Jotaro: Got ya.
( Joseph screams )
Those tentacles are so gross,
I can’t even look at ’em!
Come on, jotaro!
Just destroy the damn thing!
Jotaro: Quit your bitchin’,
old man.
Joseph: There.
Now that my grandson
has pulled out that flesh bud,
we all can be buddies.
You get it?
( Chuckles )
Jotaro: Hey, kakyoin,
don’t people who make
stupid puns all the time
get on your nerves,
or it just me?
( Kakyoin chuckles )
Joseph:
The speedwagon foundation
chartered a boat
for us yesterday.
With any luck, it’s reached
the harbor ahead of us.
( All gasp )
Avdol: We meet again.
So what’s on your mind...
Polnareff?
Polnareff: I never
thanked you properly
for freeing me
from dio’s mind control.
Avdol: Young jojo is the one
you should be thanking here.
Jotaro: Don’t need your thanks.
( Avdol chuckles )
It appears your fine manners
are wasted on the likes of us.
( Polnareff gasps )
As you wish. I’ve no desire
to come off as heavy-handed,
but i’m not quite finished here.
- Polnareff: Mssr. Joestar...
- Joseph: Eh?
Polnareff: I hope you’ll indulge
my asking
a very bizarre question.
Joseph: A bizarre question,
you say?
Polnareff: I noticed
at the restaurant yesterday
that you never took off
your gloves, even while eating.
Tell me. Your left hand
wouldn’t happen to be
a right hand under that glove?
Joseph: Huh?
Is my left hand a right one?
You weren’t kidding
about the bizarre part.
What are you hoping
to find out through all this?
♪
Polnareff:
I’m looking for the man
who murdered my younger sister.
( All gasp )
Polnareff:
I don’t know his face.
But he definitely has
two right hands
instead of one of each.
Joseph: Here.
I lost the real thing
in a horrible battle
some 50 years ago.
( Polnareff sighs )
I apologize for the rudeness.
Please forgive me.
Joseph: If it’s not
too painful to talk about,
i’d like to know what happened.
( Polnareff grunts )
It’s been three years now.
My younger sister
and a classmate of hers
were walking home from school
in the rain
back in our native France.
It was a country road,
much like any other.
On the side of the road, a man
stood with his back to them.
Oddly enough,
the mysterious stranger was dry.
The rain fell
in torrents around him,
as though
an invisible shell guarded him.
Suddenly her friend
fell to the ground
in a fountain of blood,
as though her chest
was cut by the wind.
My sister was alone.
He stole her innocence,
and then he killed her.
That was all the man wanted.
For that, she died.
Her friend escaped with her life
to tell me what she saw
that fateful day.
She didn’t get a good look
at their tormenter’s face,
but saw that both of his hands
were right hands.
No one believed the poor girl’s
testimony about the man,
no one but me, that is.
I had already been keeping
my own strange powers a secret
by then, and he sounded
like a fellow stand user.
Joseph: He’s a stand user,
all right. I’m sure of it.
Polnareff: I swore an oath!
I promised my sister’s soul
that I would avenge her,
to hunt down the killer
and make him pay with his life!
I would use my own stand as
a tool of righteous vengeance!
Then, a year ago,
my travels led me to dio.
♪
( Gasps )
That man.
The reflection shows...
Dio: It’s a vision
from your heart, not mine.
The man you seek,
the pain you hide,
my power only makes it visible.
How about it, polnareff?
Care to become friends?
( Polnareff gasps )
Dio: Tragedy gnaws away
at your soul.
I need no glass to see that.
Work with me, and your suffering
will soon be nothing more
than a thing of the past.
The image in the globe
is what pains you, is it not?
What if I could help you?
I, too,
am plagued with misfortune.
I have been denied
the sun’s embrace forevermore.
Be an agent of my will
out in the sunlight,
and I will find this man
who haunts you so.
( Polnareff screams )
After that, I was commanded
to kill all four of you.
Never once
did I question my orders.
Avdol: Even if he
hadn’t used a flesh bud,
dio is quite the master
at manipulating human beings
to carry out his bidding.
Kakyoin: Truly. And if dio
has found your sister’s killer,
we might safely assume
he’s enlisted the villain
in whatever dark plans
he’s got afoot.
Polnareff: If that is true,
I must join you on your trek
to Egypt, messieurs!
By going after dio,
I will find the one
who took my sister’s life.
Kakyoin: What do we do?
Avdol: I have no objections
to him coming.
Jotaro: Hmph.
Joseph: Even if we tell him no,
i’m sure he’ll
just follow along.
Narrator: Jean Pierre polnareff.
Stand name, silver chariot.
Powers,
fast and precise swordsmanship.
Polnareff:
The honor is all mine.
( Jotaro sighs )
Give me a break.
- Woman: Excuse me, sir.
- Jotaro: Huh?
Woman: I’m sorry,
but could I bug you
to take our picture, maybe?
( Thinking ) He’s so hot.
What a good excuse
to talk to him.
Woman #2: Please,
will you do it?
Woman #1: Oh! Oh! Take it
with the ocean behind us.
Jotaro: Shut up already!
Go bug someone else!
Polnareff: Easy, mon ami.
Ladies, I would love
to take your photograph.
Come along. There.
You have very nice legs.
I’ll be sure
to get them in the shot.
Oui. Perfection.
And another one, for safety.
Tres bien!
If only I could use this camera
to capture your hearts
instead of just your picture,
mademoiselles.
I’ve seen many beauties...
Avdol: This is nothing like
the polnareff of a moment ago.
Kakyoin: It’s like
his emotions change on a dime.
Joseph: More like
he’s got two brains,
and the one downstairs suddenly
started calling the shots.
( Jotaro groans )
Oh, give me a break.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian