♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Dan chuckles )
What a nice bridge
you make, jotaro.
( Humming a tune )
( Continues humming )
Oh, hang on.
Jotaro, I have
a very nasty itch.
Scratch it.
( Chuckles )
( Sighs )
( Moans )
Just a little lower.
Even lower.
Ah, yeah, that’s it.
But not too hard, mind you.
( Sighing )
Joseph: Huh? ( Yells )
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar?
Polnareff:
Hey, what’s the matter?
Joseph: It honestly feels like
someone’s tickling my back.
I can’t concentrate
much longer like this.
Whah! Whah! Whah!
- Aah!
- Both: Calm down!
- ( Both gasp )
- ( Crowd murmuring )
- Joseph: Enough already!
- Kakyoin: Just perfect.
We’ve got quite
the captive audience.
- Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar...
- Joseph: Make it stop!
Kakyoin: Keep your voice down.
People are staring.
Keep this up, and they’ll
think you’ve gone nuts.
Joseph: You--you think i’m
screaming for the hell of it?
Oh, no!
Man: That poor man.
Woman: Why don’t we
give him some change?
Kakyoin: W-why are
they throwing money?
( Joseph yelling )
Man #2: I pity ’em.
Older relatives like that
can be tough.
Man #3: That is so true.
( Joseph continues yelling )
Polnareff: Kakyoin,
go buy the TV.
Let’s get out of this crowd.
Kakyoin: Right.
Is this your store?
Shopkeeper: Uh, yes, it is.
Kakyoin: I’d like
to buy that TV.
( Dan sighs )
( Growls )
Unbelievable.
Kakyoin’s hierophant
and polnareff’s chariot
made themselves microscopic
and infiltrated joestar’s body.
They intend to fight me.
I can see them.
They’re traveling
through the bloodstream
and heading
toward the brainstem,
right to my lovers.
( Chuckles )
- ( Both panting )
- Kakyoin: Quickly.
We don’t have long
before the flesh bud
in Mr. Joestar’s brain
eats clean through.
Hurry, you two!
Polnareff: Allez hop!
All right.
Kakyoin: Do it, Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: Right. Hermit purple!
Hierophant green:
Th-these are...
The flesh bud’s tentacles.
Silver chariot: Great.
We’re finally at the brainstem,
but the flesh bud’s
already taken over.
Putain!
♪
( The lovers snarls )
Silver chariot: It’s him!
( The lovers yells )
( Shrieks )
Hierophant green:
Just look at that fiend.
He’s using
those weird claws of his
to knead Mr. Joestar’s
brain cells into a gooey mash,
and I bet he’s going to feed it
to the flesh bud.
We have to destroy him
and tear out all the flesh bud’s
roots as fast as we can,
or else they’ll
completely devour his brain.
Silver chariot: D’accord.
I’ll julienne him to ribbons!
You know, on second thought,
I think a finer cut
should do the trick.
I’ll turn you
into a lump of pate!
No, you don’t!
( The lovers groans )
Silver chariot: Now!
Hierophant green: He did it!
Silver chariot: No, not quite.
I gotta say, kakyoin,
that thing’s pretty fast.
But, luckily for us,
i’ve already figured him out.
If that’s all
the little beast has,
then he’s no match for--
hierophant green: Polnareff...
Who are you talking to?
Silver chariot: Wha--huh?
Hierophant green:
Polnareff, that’s not me,
and that wasn’t the real stand.
Look. It’s melting away.
( Silver chariot gasping )
What the?!
The lovers: I’m the lovers.
( Yells )
( Polnareff gags )
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
- Joseph: Polnareff.
Hierophant green:
He disguised himself
using the brain cells,
Mr. Joestar’s brain cells.
Somehow, that thing
was able to use
the collection
of kneaded brain cells
to disguise himself
as my hierophant green!
And since he can mold
his cells at will,
all you destroyed was a decoy
made of those brain cells.
The lovers:
You hit the nail on the head.
And you dummies
completely fell for it.
( Laughs )
( Men gasping )
( Dan laughing )
Come on.
Pull your head
out of your ass, would you?
You better shine those shoes
right, jotaro.
I’m in such a good mood,
I can hardly stand it,
so i’m gonna need you
to keep polishing these shoes
until they’re shining
as brightly as I feel right now.
Do you think
you can handle that,
my little sycophant?
You can stop polishing
when that magnificent sun
up in the sky
makes these puppies sparkle.
Also, I want you to use
your tongue to shine them.
Hey, you bastard,
what are you writing in there?
Jotaro: You’re looking
at your tab,
and you’re gonna pay in full.
I wrote it down
so I won’t forget.
♪
( Dan growls )
You’re a scoundrel, jotaro.
Heh.
Well, it doesn’t matter.
It’ll all be meaningless
in the end.
Silver chariot: Whoa!
Kakyoin, look!
Check out the decoy’s head
that I just opened.
( Hierophant green gasps )
♪
Joseph: What?
What the hell’s going on?
Somehow he’s splitting in two.
( The lovers laughs )
Listen up.
Here’s some advice.
To win in life, one must
thoroughly know oneself.
It’s like aesop’s fables,
when the unassuming tortoise
beats the hare.
The tortoise outruns the hare,
because he knows himself
and his abilities
better than anyone else.
Of course,
the same applies to me.
I’m no fool.
I know perfectly well
I don’t possess
the power or speed necessary
to mortally wound
either of you one-on-one,
but remember this.
The spoils belong to those
who admit their own weaknesses!
Hierophant green:
Emerald splash!
Silver chariot: Did it work?
( All gasp )
Hierophant green: What?
More decoys are forming
out of the brain cells.
They’re multiplying.
But a person
can have only one stand,
which means
only one of them is real.
That said,
where’s the real one?
The lovers: Right here!
( Polnareff gags )
Hierophant green:
Emerald splash!
The lovers:
Well, that’s not good.
Any closer,
and I would have been killed.
( Hierophant green gasps )
The more decoys we hit,
the more they multiply.
Decoys: No, no.
It’s me. It’s me.
It’s me. It’s me. It’s me.
They’re all me. Can’t you tell?
( Polnareff gasping )
Joseph: Polnareff,
that’s enough.
Withdraw your stand now.
I can’t just watch you
get hurt,
even if you are
trying to save me.
( Polnareff speaks French )
I can’t stand
the thought of giving up
and watching you die like this.
Joseph: Are you trying to die?
Withdraw your stand.
Do as I say. It’s over.
Kakyoin: You can’t quit,
Mr. Joestar.
We’ll fight till the end.
( Joseph grunts )
Kakyoin: Damn.
They all look the same.
Which one is the real one,
and which one of them
is the stand?
I can’t tell them apart.
( The lovers laughs )
The world’s weakest stand is...
Decoys: The most, the most,
the most, the most,
the most,
the most, the most, the most,
the most, the most,
the most,
the most, the most, the most,
the most, the most,
the most,
the most, the most, the most,
the most powerful of all!
( All yell )
( Dan laughs )
Hey, now,
take a look at this, jotaro.
It’s beautiful, isn’t it?
I would wager
an expensive gift like this
would make any girl
fall head over heels.
Jotaro...
You see that space there
in the glass?
Use your stand to sneak through
and steal the bracelet.
♪
Steal it.
What don’t you understand,
moron?
Get a move on,
if you know what’s good for you.
I mean, I don’t mind
breaking the glass
and taking
the bracelet myself.
Then again, if i’m caught,
I could be beaten
to a bloody pulp.
Old Joseph would surely die
from the pain.
( Jotaro groans )
Dan: Hurry, would you?
Do it while the salesman’s
looking the other way.
( Dan chuckles )
Oh, no! This guy is shoplifting!
- ( Salesman gasps )
- ( Jotaro gasps )
( Dan laughs )
Jotaro: Son of a...
( Dan chuckling )
Dan: Do something!
This guy’s shoplifting!
Come on, salesman!
Salesman: I’ll go
and get some help!
Please, sir,
don’t let him get away!
Dan: Sure thing. ( Chuckles )
Jotaro: Bastard.
Man: All right, boys,
where is this thief at?
Man #2: Who’s the culprit?
Is it that guy there?
Man #1: You talkin’
about that Asian kid?
You know,
back where I come from,
when someone steals somethin’.
We chop their fingers off
Dan: Hey, jotaro...
You better not use your stand
against civilians.
Man #1: Punk!
- Take this!
- Man #3: Despicable!
Man #2: You dirty thief!
( Dan laughs )
Man #2: Now you get the hell
out of our country,
and don’t come back.
Good for nothin’ asshole.
Man #1: You do that, and we’ll
allow you to leave here
with your fingers intact.
( Man #2 spits )
( Men laugh )
( Dan laughing )
That was great.
Nicely done, my friend.
Thanks to the commotion
you caused,
I was able to get my hands
on something
even better than that bracelet.
( Jotaro chuckling )
Dan: Huh?
( Jotaro laughing )
Dan: Jotaro, what the hell
are you laughing about?
What’s so damn funny?!
( Jotaro chuckles )
Nothing. I’m just a bit excited.
I was laughing, because
your punishment has doubled,
and i’ve been waiting a while
for this moment.
It’s just about time
for payback,
and I gotta say
it’s really got me tingling.
Dan: Why, you...
It would seem...
That we have something
of a misunderstanding.
I’m sorry to say,
but your old man
isn’t long for this world.
That’s the reality
you’re facing.
( Jotaro chuckles )
How sad. You don’t know us
very well, do you, friend?
And I see you don’t know
kakyoin at all.
Dan: Come again?
Kakyoin: It seems to me
you’re obsessed
with the notion
of knowing oneself.
Yes, that makes sense.
I suppose i’m inclined to agree.
But before you
continue pontificating,
think on this for a moment.
There’s another adage,
"know thy enemy,"
that’s nothing to scoff at.
Can’t you see? My hierophant
has a certain ability.
It has the power
to stretch out its feelers,
and i’ve been inspecting
every single one of you.
The lovers: Gah!
How could I have not noticed
something touching me?
Hierophant green:
So you’re the stand.
Emerald splash!
Both: Success!
( Dan gagging )
Jotaro: Well, well,
what do we have here?
Looks like kakyoin
got you pretty damn good.
So i’m wondering, will I get
my payback once he’s done?
( Dan stammers )
( Shrieks )
♪
Silver chariot: He realized
that he’s out of his league,
and now he’s trying
to escape into the artery.
Hierophant green:
He’s trying to escape
from Mr. Joestar’s brain.
Joseph: Huh?
Did you say he’s leaving?
Polnareff: All right.
That’s great news, isn’t it?
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar, hurry,
the flesh bud.
Joseph: Right.
Time for overdrive!
Silver chariot:
The flesh bud’s vanishing.
( Joseph sighs )
Thank god it’s gone.
( Both sigh )
Polnareff: Well, if you ask me,
this whole experience
has done a lot to bring
our group closer together.
Joseph: You’re incorrigible,
polnareff.
( Gasps ) Hold on a minute.
If that thing’s really
trying to leave my brain...
Then wouldn’t that imply
that the stand is...
( Polnareff gasps )
The bastard is returning
to its user!
Joseph: This is bad.
Jotaro’s has no way of knowing.
( Dan gasping )
Jotaro: What’s wrong?
Why are you
backing away from me?
Aren’t you going to tell me more
about my grandfather’s death?
I’d really love to know.
Hey, wait a minute.
What’s with the big hurry?
We weren’t done talking yet.
No, it couldn’t be.
You’re not actually trying
to run away, are you,
after all you’ve done?
( Dan stammering )
( Yelps )
Please jotaro, sir, forgive me.
I admit it. You win.
I’ll lie down
and lick your boots.
I know I did a bad thing,
and I wanna change.
( Sobs )
You can pummel me as much
as you’d like.
Hit me, kick me,
but, please, don’t kill me.
I’m begging you
to spare my life.
Lick, lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick,
lick, lick, lick...
Soon, very soon,
the lovers will return to me,
and this idiot jotaro
doesn’t have a single clue.
Just you wait. This time,
it’ll enter your brain.
Kakyoin can’t help you
from hundreds of meters away.
I’ll make you suffer
pain so horrible,
you’ll wish you were never born.
Heh. It’s here.
It’s here. It’s here.
Now, enter his ear.
( Star platinum yells )
Ora!
♪
( Dan screams )
Jotaro: I kinda figured
you’d go and try
something shitty like this.
Don’t you know my stand,
star platinum,
possesses excellent eyesight
and precise reflexes?
You’re pathetic.
Didn’t you check up on us
at all, even a little bit?
Dan: No, no, no, no, no.
Believe me,
I wasn’t planning anything,
not against your stand’s
immense power.
Jotaro: Did you
just say, "your stand"?
Only "your"?
Dan: Let me explain.
W-what I meant to say is that
your awesome and powerful stand
is far superior to any other.
I knew it didn’t stand a chance,
so I had it come back.
Just look at what you’ve done.
You’ve already shattered
my arm and leg to pieces.
I can’t possibly fight anymore.
I can’t even move.
( Cracking )
( Screams )
Jotaro: In that case...
I guess i’ll take pity on you
and accept
your arm and leg as payment
for all the low blows
you took out against me,
but only if you swear
that you’ll never show
your ugly mug
in front of us again.
Dan: I’ll do whatever you say.
I promise.
I’ll head
for some deserted island,
or i’ll go
to the ends of the earth
and never return to bother you.
Jotaro:
You’d better not be lying.
The next time I see that face,
it’ll get a thousand punches.
Dan: I’m not lying.
I would never, ever lie to you.
Jotaro: Get lost.
( Dan growls )
Boy: Let’s play soccer
over there.
( Children chattering )
( Dan grunts )
Jotaro.
( Laughs )
You’re an utter fool.
Just take a look at that girl.
Girl: Well,
I wanna play over here.
Dan: It might interest you
to know that my stand,
the lovers, just went
into that girl’s ear.
Now he’s heading for her brain.
You better not move, jotaro.
( Laughs )
Here’s what’s about to happen.
I’m gonna stab you in the back
with this knife
and make sure that you’re
never able to move again.
Attack me
with your star platinum,
and this girl’s pathetic life
ends right here and now.
But you would never allow
such an innocent child
to die, would you?
( Laughs )
( Jotaro growls )
Oh, good grief.
Go ahead, and stab me, then.
Dan: Huh?
Hey, now, did you not hear me?
I just told you not to--
I told...
You not...To move.
( Gasping )
Jotaro: What’s the matter?
Didn’t you say something
about stabbing me?
Like this, right?
( Dan screams )
My--my body won’t move!
W-why?
The lovers: What the--
what is this thing
wrapped around me?
Jotaro: I see you didn’t notice.
As your stand was trying
to make its escape,
kakyoin tied hierophant’s
tentacle to its leg.
And seeing as those tentacles
stretch all the way
back to your stand
like a string to a kite,
you must have been
so self-absorbed,
you didn’t even notice.
♪
( Children laughing )
( Dan gasping )
Please, i’m begging you,
forgive me!
Joseph: Ask for forgiveness
from enyaba,
the woman you killed.
But as for me,
I never had the slightest
intention of forgiving you.
( Dan groans )
D-dio paid me
to cause this madness.
Y-you can have it all.
Jotaro: Good grief. I know
this is blatantly obvious,
but you really are
a piece of work.
What you owe me
can never be paid back
with money!
Star platinum: Ora! ( Yelling )
♪
Jotaro: Your receipt.
Keep the change if you want.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian