♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Fire crackling )
Jotaro: So this is Saudi Arabia,
about 8,800 kilometers
from Japan.
And it’s been around four weeks
since we began our journey.
If we don’t hurry,
we’ll be in serious trouble.
Kakyoin.
Polnareff: Hey, jotaro. What do
you think is up with kakyoin?
First he nearly
kills us in his sleep.
Now he looks like he’s
coming apart at the seams.
He even went after the baby.
Something’s just not right.
If you ask me,
he’s at his wit’s end.
( Baby hisses )
( Chuckles )
For a second there, I thought
he’d actually figured me out,
but now the poor louse
is half-doubting himself.
To top things off, we’re
in the middle of the desert.
All I have to do is wait
until they fall asleep.
If there’s no one
to wake them up...
( Laughs )
Polnareff:
Something smells good.
What kind of food is that?
Joseph: This is baby food.
It’s a delicious concoction
of milk, egg yolks,
bananas, and bread
all stewed together.
So you wanna taste it?
( Polnareff gulps )
Joseph: Hmm?
Polnareff: Wow!
This is flat-out amazing!
Give me more!
Joseph: Easy now.
At this rate, there won’t
be any left for the baby.
Baby: You incompetent bastard,
how dare you eat my food?
I’m wasting away over here,
so hurry up,
and feed me, damn it.
( Groans )
( Yelps )
It’s--it’s a scorpion.
♪
What am I going to do?
( Gasps )
( Sighs )
That was a close one.
( Gasps )
( Kakyoin shuddering )
Baby: Crap baskets.
Kakyoin was watching.
Kakyoin: He killed the scorpion.
So I was right.
That baby really is a...
Baby: Shit. What now?
Joseph: You’re not
getting any more.
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar,
polnareff, did you see that?
Both: Huh?
Kakyoin: I was right after all.
That baby’s not normal.
He just killed a scorpion.
He stabbed it.
The boy skewered it
with his own safety pin.
- Joseph: Eh?
- Polnareff: Eh?
Joseph: Kakyoin, hold on a sec.
What the hell
are you talking about?
The baby, damn it.
That kid isn’t human.
He’s not even a year old yet,
but he knew what a scorpion was,
and he killed it
with those tiny hands of his.
Joseph: A scorpion?
Where is it?
- Kakyoin: It’s in here.
- Joseph: Huh?
Kakyoin: Where’d it go?
There should be
an impaled scorpion here.
Joseph: Hmm.
Kakyoin: It’s gone.
( Joseph scoffs )
Kakyoin: I swear it’s true.
He must have
hidden it somewhere!
Check his clothes!
Joseph: We get the point.
Knock it off, kakyoin.
That’s enough.
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: Like I said before,
you’re clearly exhausted.
- Kakyoin: But--
- Joseph: Let’s table this,
at least for tonight.
We’ll talk
after you’ve calmed down.
( Kakyoin gasps )
( Polnareff groans )
♪
( Joseph blowing )
Okay, here’s the choo-choo.
It’s dewicious.
Uh-oh. What’s the matter?
You were hungry
a minute ago, right?
Did you lose that big appetite?
Ahh...
Baby: Would you stop
shoving that spoon in my face?
I can’t eat right now,
you idiot!
Joseph: Huh?
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar, listen!
I’m not imagining things.
I don’t know where he could have
hidden the blasted scorpion,
but i’m sure
that he’s a stand user,
and I have just the thing
to prove to you
that i’m telling the truth.
Do you see these cuts?
Read what the letters spell out.
Can’t you see
that it’s a warning?
It must have happened to me
when I was sleeping earlier.
Joseph: Oh, my god!
( Baby gasps )
Jotaro: Kakyoin, you didn’t
do that to yourself, did you?
Kakyoin: Say what?
Polnareff: I-it’s finally
happened. Kakyoin.
Joseph: Oh, my god.
♪
Baby: You colossal buffoon.
How stupid can you be?
Didn’t you realize
if you showed them
the cuts on your arm,
they’d think you were crazy?
Kakyoin: What’s going on?
Did I make things even worse?
Then it looks like
I have no other choice.
I’ll have to rely on force.
Hierophant green!
( Baby wails )
( Kakyoin groans )
Polnareff: It’s no use.
Damn it. The guy has
completely lost his mind.
Kakyoin: This can’t
be happening.
I’m certain of what I saw,
jotaro.
His stand was the one we fought
in our dreams, polnareff.
We can’t fall asleep,
Mr. Joestar.
Believe me, everyone,
if we fall asleep,
we’ll all be killed.
Please, you guys...
You have to believe me.
Baby: Yes!
My secret is still safe,
which means the end is near.
Your petty mistrust
just cost you your lives.
Victory is mine, fools.
Polnareff: I can’t believe it.
If he’s like this,
does that mean kakyoin
can’t fight or travel
with us anymore?
( Joseph sighs )
We’ll discuss it in the morning.
Let’s get some sleep.
Polnareff,
give me a hand moving kakyoin.
Polnareff: Sure thing.
Joseph: Jotaro,
you bring the sleeping bags.
Jotaro: Right.
( Baby gags )
Joseph: You say something?
Polnareff: No.
He’s just really heavy.
Baby: I’ve got you
right where I want you.
I’m gonna slice you up
and scatter your remains
all over the desert.
( Spits )
♪
( Polnareff snoring )
Joseph: Hmm?
What in the world?
Why are we in the middle
of an amusement park?
We were just out in the desert.
- Polnareff: That’s right.
- Joseph: Eh?
I know this place.
Jotaro, Mr. Joestar,
be on your guard.
M-my memory is coming back.
We’ve been transported
to a dream world...
A horrible one.
This is bad.
We’ve entered
a world of nightmares.
Joseph:
Oh, so it’s a dream, huh?
You had me a little worried
for a minute there.
Polnareff: Don’t make
the same mistake that I did!
Listen, everything kakyoin
said to us earlier is true.
Baby...stand.
We are in enemy territory.
I know this may be hard
for you to believe,
but the stand user is that baby.
There’s no one left to wake you
from your slumber now,
and that means
there’s absolutely no way
for you to escape
death 13’s world.
I’ll finally finish you off
once and for all.
♪
Polnareff: Why did I have to hit
kakyoin and knock him out?
But since I did that...
He should already be here!
We’ve got to find him.
Where in the world
are you, kakyoin?!
I have to find a way
to make this up to you.
Joseph: P-polnareff!
Good lord, what is
going on with your hair?!
Did you mess up brushing it?!
Polnareff: Huh?
( Yells )
( Screaming )
Joseph: Polnareff!
Jotaro: What the...
Joseph: Ahh! What’s going on?
My prosthetic hand is...
Yah!
Holy shit bricks!
( Groans )
( Laughter )
Polnareff: How are we
supposed to fight this?
It’s maddening.
Damn, anything can happen
in this world.
There are no rules here.
Nothing makes sense.
As long as we’re in this place,
we’re completely at his mercy.
Wait. I remember
there being one rule...
His murder weapon.
If he wants
to slice us to pieces,
then he’ll have to use
his stand...
And nothing but his stand.
Death 13: Lali-ho!
( All gasping )
Jotaro: Ora! Star...
Polnareff: Jotaro, it’s no use!
It’s impossible for us to bring
our stands into this world!
Jotaro: Platinum!
( Polnareff gasps )
That’s weird.
His stand manifested.
( Star platinum grunts )
( Yelling )
Ora!
( Jotaro groans )
( Star platinum laughs )
Ora?
Ora.
( Babbles )
( Grunts ) Ora?
Ora. ( Laughs )
Death 13: Lali-ho.
Surprise. I’m a fake.
Oh, the overwhelming power,
the absolute terror,
it’s so much fun!
A stand is
a manifestation of the mind,
and what are dreams
if not the mind laid bare?
My death 13 has trapped you
within your subconscious,
which is why you can’t summon
your precious stands.
Although...
Things might be different
had you summoned your stands
before you fell asleep.
( Head rattles )
Then, they would have
appeared here with you,
just like your clothes,
sleeping bags,
and your prosthetic hand.
Death 13 will never be forced
to face another stand in battle.
And, as you know, the only thing
that can defeat a stand
is another stand,
so i’ll always come out on top.
( Laughs )
Now that I have all of you
in my cross hairs,
how about you give me a scream,
one that captures the joy
and elation i’m about to feel
at my easy victory?!
( Men gasp )
Death 13: Lali--ho?
Oh, it’s just one
of the fakes I made.
♪
( Gags )
What? I don’t understand.
This one doesn’t seem
to be a fake.
This is the real hierophant.
( Coughs )
Joseph: It’s normal.
Polnareff: Look! It’s kakyoin.
Kakyoin’s right there.
Kakyoin: Obviously
it slipped your notice
that i’d already summoned
my hierophant
by the time
I was knocked unconscious.
What’s more,
I had it burrow underground
to conceal itself from detection
just before I fell asleep.
( Death 13 groans )
You can’t do this.
Kakyoin: Now, it’s time
for your punishment, baby.
( Manishu gagging )
Damn that bastard.
( Death 13 yelling )
Let go!
Kakyoin: Give up, death 13.
I had hierophant place himself
in your blind spot.
If you keep up
this futile struggling...
Regardless of the fact
you’re a baby,
it’ll snap your neck
like a twig.
Joseph: Kakyoin!
- ( Kakyoin grunts )
- Joseph: Kakyoin,
the three of us
owe you an enormous apology.
Polnareff: I thought
after the hell
you’d been through on this trip,
you might have suddenly
lost your sanity.
I mean, a baby stand user?
You were fighting
this battle alone,
and for that, i’m sorry.
Kakyoin: Don’t worry, polnareff.
It couldn’t have been helped.
You were the reason
I found a way
to bring my stand
to the dream world with me.
If you hadn’t hit me,
we’d be stuck here
without a way
to defend ourselves,
so, in a way,
this is all thanks to you.
Polnareff: Yeah?
Do you mean that?
Gee, now I feel conflicted
about the whole thing.
That’s embarrassing.
( Giggling )
( Manishu gagging )
Kakyoin hasn’t killed me yet,
because i’m a baby.
( Laughs )
Kakyoin, your compassion
will cost you your life.
In case you’ve forgotten,
you’re all still trapped
inside my nightmare world.
♪
( Kakyoin gasps )
Polnareff: Uh-oh.
What’s up with these clouds?
Joseph: No kidding.
They’re changing shape
and closing in.
Kakyoin: You’d better not
try anything funny, death 13.
Jotaro: Kakyoin,
you have to get hierophant
away from his back
before it’s too late.
Kakyoin: How did--
death 13: I’ll chop you in half!
Kakyoin: Impossible.
How could he do that?
He--he chopped himself in half.
All: Kakyoin! No!
Death 13: Lali-ho.
Haven’t you figured it out yet?
Death 13’s body is as hollow
as the space between your ears.
Manishu: My stand
is only comprised
of the head, arms,
and the giant scythe it wields.
You gigantic ignoramuses.
Let’s see.
Given the way the stands work,
kakyoin’s body
should also be split in two
inside the sleeping bag.
Kakyoin: Nah, just kidding.
All: Kakyoin!
Joseph: Hey,
you sure you’re all right?
Kakyoin: Hah.
Please take a closer look.
Surely you know hierophant
isn’t that careless.
He wouldn’t just stay
on the enemy’s back
without a plan in the wings.
( Death 13 gasps )
( Shuddering )
Manishu:
He’s not chopped in half.
He’s turned into
a snakelike thing,
and he’s slithering into my ear!
♪
( Death 13 yelling )
My arm is moving on its own!
( Yelling )
No! It’s coming in!
Kakyoin: I told you before,
my stand was in your blind spot,
and your scythe
couldn’t cut him.
Now, then, unless you’d
like to be destroyed
from the inside out,
how about you do me a favor
and heal the cuts on my arm?
Anything is possible
in a dream, right?
So healing a cut should be easy.
Death 13: R-right.
( Sizzling )
Kakyoin: All right, everyone,
time to wake up.
- ( All grumbling )
- ( Clangs pan )
( Polnareff groans )
Kakyoin: Come on, polnareff.
Up and at ’em.
There’s a nice breakfast
waiting for you.
Polnareff: I feel like I had
a terrible dream last night.
Joseph: You and me both.
I can’t remember it, but I
have the sneaking suspicion
that it was terrifying.
( Polnareff gasps ) Kakyoin.
Are you okay?
How are you feeling?
Kakyoin: I’m fine.
Polnareff: What?
Are you positive?
’cause you were acting like
a deranged lunatic last night.
You even carved letters
in your...
Arm.
Wait. What?
Where did the wound go?
Kakyoin: All right, I think i’ll
change the baby’s diaper now.
Polnareff: What in the world?
Kakyoin:
It’s morning, sleepyhead.
Polnareff: He seems to be
getting along famously
with the baby.
Maybe I just dreamed
the whole thing.
( Kakyoin laughs )
Well, then,
did you have a good rest?
Polnareff: Oh, well. Never mind.
Kakyoin: Mm-hmm.
( Manishu gasping )
Kakyoin: Everyone’s forgotten.
A stand whose very existence
is completely forgotten,
what a strange creature.
But I haven’t
forgotten anything.
Since I brought my stand
into the dream with me,
my memories are intact.
Listen,
because you’re just a baby,
I won’t eliminate you.
I won’t even injure you.
We’ll take you to a nearby town.
You need to be returned
to your mother.
However, don’t come
anywhere near us again.
If you do,
you’ll have to be punished...
In a manner such as this.
Manishu: Huh? Is that my poop?
( Gasping )
Joseph: Oh, kakyoin.
I see you’ve made some
baby food for the little lad.
Kakyoin: Yes.
Joseph: Good work. I’m sure
he must be starving by now.
Manishu: Hey, no, you wouldn’t.
♪
Joseph: Eat up.
These yum-yums are dewicious.
Say, "ahh."
Ahh.
This again? What’s the problem?
It’s as if he
doesn’t like the stuff.
At this rate,
i’ll have to force-feed him.
Manishu: Stop!
Polnareff: You can’t force it,
Mr. Joestar.
If you do, he’ll just end up
hating it even more.
In special cases like this...
( Manishu grunting )
Polnareff: Ah, coochie-coo.
Ah, coochie-coochie-
coochie-coochie-coo.
coochie-coo.
( Manishu wails )
( Swallows )
( Crying )
Joseph: I told you
it was delicious.
Kakyoin: Ba-dum-bum.
♪
Narrator: Joestar and the others
have now crossed
the arabian peninsula
and are currently making
their way across the red sea
as they prepare to enter Egypt,
but...
Jotaro: Hey, old man,
something’s off.
You’re going
the wrong direction.
If you’re headed to Egypt,
shouldn’t you be traveling
directly west?
Both: Hmm?
Jotaro: You seem to be heading
toward that island.
Joseph: That’s right.
Nice deduction.
I’ve had my reasons
for keeping this to myself,
but before we arrive in Egypt,
we need to make a slight detour.
Someone is waiting for us
on the island.
- Kakyoin: Huh?
- Polnareff: Hmm.
Joseph: He’s a man
who is extremely important
to our journey.
Polnareff: What is that
supposed to mean?
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian