Narrator: Previously
on "jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
Avdol: Mrs. Kujo has
materialized her own stand!
Gray fly: I’ll keep you
from lord dio
if it’s the last thing I do.
Avdol: But if we fail
to find dio within 50 days...
Polnareff:
Someone I know has a Mark,
a birthmark just like this
on the back of their neck.
Know anyone like that?
What?!
( Screams )
If that is true,
I must join you on your trek
to Egypt, messieurs.
By going after dio,
I will find the one
who took my sister’s life!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: The loathsome
curse of dio.
Even the speedwagon foundation’s
leading physicians
with their
cutting-edge treatments
stand powerless
before dio’s curse.
( Doctor sighs )
Narrator: To save Holly,
jojo and crew
continue on their journey
to Egypt.
With air travel
now too treacherous,
they board a boat,
heading first to Singapore.
Joseph: To get
from Hong Kong to Singapore,
we’ll be on the water
for three full days.
Well, let’s relax
and keep our spirits up.
But first,
I have a serious question.
What the hell is with
the high school uniforms,
you two?
Can’t you go and find
something else to put on?
Isn’t it ridiculously hot?
Kakyoin: Well,
we are students, after all,
and good students
should behave as such,
no matter where they are,
but I guess that sounds
like a stretch.
Jotaro: Hmph.
Joseph: Hah!
Japanese students are
such stiffs, aren’t they?
Avdol: So this is
what they call bushido.
Like they say, clear your mind,
and even flames feel cool.
Polnareff:
That’s all well and good,
but that really
won’t get you any girls.
- Child: Let go!
- Polnareff: Huh?
Child: Let go of me!
Damn it, I said get off of me!
- Sailor: Shut your trap!
- Child: Let me go!
- What’s your problem?
- Sailor: You brat!
Joseph: Hey, who’s that?
I thought we agreed
there’d be no other passengers
onboard but us.
Sailor: Sorry, sir.
It’s a stowaway.
This little brat was hiding in
one of the storage holds below.
Joseph: Stowaway?
Child: What you waitin’ for?
Come at me!
I’ll fricking break your balls!
Sailor: Tell that to the police,
you little shit. I dare you.
Child: What? The police?
Wait. I’m sorry, all right?
Please, just let me go.
I just wanted to go to Singapore
to see my dad. That’s all.
I’ll do anything. You could even
put me to work for my ticket.
( Winces )
Sailor: Let’s see.
What should I do?
Should I let you go
or turn you in?
- What to do? What to do?
- Child: You gotta let me go!
Please!
Sailor: We could use
another cabin boy.
No way i’m letting you go.
That’s too easy.
( Child whimpers )
Sailor: But first,
i’m gonna let the captain know.
( Screams )
♪
Polnareff: Whoa. In he goes.
That kid’s got guts.
Kakyoin: Is he planning
to swim to shore from out here?
Joseph: What should we do?
( Jotaro scoffs )
Just leave him.
He wouldn’t have dived in
if he wasn’t a good swimmer.
( Sailor gasps )
No, he’s in danger!
This entire area
is infested with sharks!
( Joseph gasps )
Kakyoin: This isn’t good.
Joseph: Hey, kid, come back!
It’s dangerous! You’ll die!
Polnareff: Listen to us!
There’s sharks out there!
( Child whimpers )
( Screams )
Star platinum:
Ora, ora, ora!
( Child gasps )
( Blows striking )
( Jotaro chuckles )
Good grief. Come on, you brat.
- ( Gasps )
- ( Child gasps )
( Shuddering )
Jotaro: Hold on.
A girl?
And a runty one, at that.
Just my luck.
Girl: Hey, how dare you feel
me up like that, you bastard?!
Hands off!
( Growls )
Jotaro: Good grief, kid.
♪
Joseph: Huh?
( Creature snarls )
Joseph: Hey, jotaro, below you!
Something’s coming after you
from underwater.
It’s not a shark,
and it’s racing towards you!
You have to get
out of there now!
Hurry! Swim to the boat!
Avdol: He’s too far away.
Kakyoin: If it’s
at that distance,
leave it to my hierophant green!
( Girl gasps )
( Polnareff gasps )
( Avdol groans )
Polnareff: It just disappeared!
That thing is a stand!
Avdol: Stunning,
an aquatic stand.
In all my dealings
with the occult,
i’ve never heard
of such a thing.
( Girl panting )
Joseph: This girl,
there’s no way she’s the...
Polnareff: Could she
be that stand’s user?
Kakyoin: Did she
try to lead jojo
into shark-infested waters
on purpose?
Girl: Eh? Jeez,
what’s with you jerks?
Stop staring like that.
It’s creepy.
I have no idea
what’s going on here,
but i’ll fight you!
Don’t underestimate me, okay?
You’re gonna regret this.
One-on-one. Come at me!
I dare you, you punks.
Polnareff: Is she playing us?
Maybe we should
toss her back into the ocean.
Kakyoin: Calm down.
If she is just a stowaway
and gets eaten by sharks,
it’d be bad,
Joseph: We’ve already checked
the 10 people on this boat.
I’m positive
they’re all in the clear.
I don’t know who it could be,
other than this girl.
Isn’t there a way we could
find out who she really is?
( Avdol grunts )
Hey, how is dio doing
these days?
Girl: Dio, huh?
What the hell is that?
Polnareff: Don’t pretend
like you don’t know,
you little brat.
Girl: Hey, I warned you, punks.
You gonna be a man
and talk to me,
or do you just want to get
shanked? Which is it, huh?
My demon blade wants the blood
of its 340th victim,
and you all
look like prime cuts.
- ( Kakyoin chuckles )
- ( Girl groans )
What’s so funny,
stupid jerk hole?!
Kakyoin: Jerk hole?
I’m starting to get the feeling
she’s not our stand user.
Joseph: Yes, but who, then?
Captain: Is this girl
our stowaway?
Thanks for grabbing her for me.
Girl: Huh? ( Screams )
♪
Joseph: Whoa, captain.
Captain: I’m pretty strict
when it comes to stowaways
on my ship here.
- Girl: You’re hurting me!
- Captain: You may be a girl,
but if I go easy on you,
we’ll just get
more and more stowaways.
I think we’ll lock you up
in the brig below deck
- until we make it to port.
- ( Girl yells )
Joseph: Hey, captain,
i’d like to ask you something.
You verified the identities
of all 10 men onboard,
haven’t you?
Captain: Of course.
They’re all veterans,
each one of them on this ship
for over 10 years.
I’ll vouch for every single man.
I’m not sure why
you’re so worried about that,
since I gave you my word
from the very beginning.
Oh, by the way...
( Jotaro gasps )
Captain: I must request
that you not smoke on deck.
What were you planning on doing
with the ash and butt
after you were done?
Were you just going to toss them
into these pristine waters?
You may be a guest on this ship,
but you will abide by my rules.
You got that?
( All gasp )
( Cigarette crinkles )
Captain: You got it, kid?
Jotaro: Hold it, pops.
If you don’t want me
to smoke aboard ship,
then just tell me.
Don’t be a condescending prick
about the whole thing,
you jackass.
Captain: Eh?
Joseph: Hey, jotaro,
don’t be disrespectful
to the captain.
You’re the one at fault.
( Jotaro chuckles )
His rules don’t mean shit.
I’ll be as rude as I want,
and you know why?
The captain is the stand user.
Joseph: Wha?!
All: What the?!
Captain: A stand...User?
I’m not sure I follow you.
What is that?
Avdol: That is
completely impossible, jotaro.
We chose captain dragon,
because he came recommended
with verification
by the speedwagon foundation.
He’s someone that we can trust.
There’s no chance
that he’s a stand user.
( Jotaro scoffs )
Captain: Hold on.
What’s this thing, a stand?
I’ve no idea what you guys
are talking about.
Polnareff: Jojo, random guesses
will only make things
more confusing!
Kakyoin: Do you have
any real proof, jojo?
Jotaro: I’ve found a way
to differentiate stand users
from others.
- Joseph: What?
- Jotaro: The trick is
to watch a possible stand user
around cigarette smoke,
because a single whiff...
Makes a vein pop up
on their nose.
Men: Huh?
Girl: What the hell
are they all doing?
Polnareff:
You’re not serious, jotaro!
Jotaro: Relax. I’m lying.
That said, it looks like
we found the idiot, didn’t we?
- ( Captain yells )
- ( Men gasp )
Girl: Huh? Huh?
♪
Captain: Hmm.
( Chuckles )
Joseph: Quite impressive,
but what tipped you off
that it was the captain?
Jotaro: Actually,
I really didn’t have a clue.
Joseph: Huh?
Jotaro: However,
i’d planned to try this
with the entire crew
from the moment we arrived.
Simple as that.
Captain: And I fell for it.
Didn’t expect this,
but, damn, you’re good.
You’re right.
I’m not the captain.
The real captain’s already
sleeping with the fishes
at the bottom of the China sea.
Jotaro: If that’s true,
then you can sleep
in the depths of hell,
you bastard.
( Captain chuckles )
( Girl screams )
Men: Damn it! No!
Girl: Let me go!
I can’t move!
( Yells )
Narrator: Trouble on the water,
lies and betrayal--
the moon card represents
the fear of the unknown.
Its name, dark blue moon.
Captain: I kept
my identity hidden,
hoping to pick you off
one by one.
Five-on-one is so troublesome,
even for me.
The other way
would have been much simpler.
But since you’ve figured me out,
I have no choice.
Five-on-one, it is.
Getting my hands on her
just shows that lady luck
is on my side.
Think i’ll take a dip
in these shark-infested waters
with the runt.
If you wanna save her,
you’re gonna
have to dive in after us.
In the ocean,
I have the advantage.
I can take on all five of you.
( Laughs )
Jotaro: Go on. Act tough
while you hide behind a hostage.
It’ll take a lot more than that
to shake me up, you dumb-ass.
Captain: It’s no act.
This is a prediction.
I hear your stand,
star platinum, is fast.
I’d like to put that
to the test.
I’m not trying to brag,
but my dark blue moon
is king underwater.
It’s much swifter
than any fish in the sea
and certainly faster than
a vulgar meathead like you.
( Laughs )
Why don’t we test
them out right now?
Come on. Follow me.
If you’re not afraid of a...
Little saltwater.
( Girl screams )
Star platinum: Ora!
( Yelling )
Captain: Ehh. He attacked me
faster than we could fall.
That’s impossible for a human.
How’d he--
jotaro: You’re the only one
who’s swallowin’
saltwater today, pops.
Choke on it. Tell him, avdol.
Avdol: Your folly was trying
to outpredict a fortuneteller.
Tough break.
Polnareff: Well said, avdol.
Polnareff: There he goes.
He talked up his stand’s power
so much, I expected more,
but in the end,
he was just a blabbering idiot.
Joseph:
What’s the matter, jotaro?
Hurry and pull the girl
out already, would you?
( Jotaro gasping )
Joseph: What’s wrong?
Do you need a hand with her?
Jotaro: Damn it.
I’m being pulled in.
( Polnareff gasps )
Avdol: Th-those are...
Kakyoin: They’re barnacles.
They’re a type of crustacean
that lives
between high and low tides.
Joseph: They’re
on star platinum’s arm,
and they’ve got him stuck
to the side of the boat.
Jotaro: He’s still got
some fight left in him.
He must have attached them
when I hit him before.
Damn things keep multiplying.
My stand’s strength,
it’s being drained.
Joseph:
The captain’s disappeared.
I can’t see him
in the water anymore.
Jotaro, pull in your stand
right now.
Jotaro: What do you think
i’m trying to do?
That’s why i’m sweating
like a freakin pig, old man!
Men: Jotaro!
Kakyoin: Jojo!
♪
Joseph: Crap! He fell in!
Kakyoin: We’ve--we’ve gotta...
Star platinum: Ora.
( Groans )
Jotaro: Hmm?
Captain: Hah.
Welcome, landlubber.
( Chuckles )
Glad you could join me
in the watery depths.
It’s where dark blue moon reigns
supreme, the undersea realm.
( Jotaro groans )
Captain: Bad idea
to underestimate me, brother.
Could be deadly.
Since we can talk underwater
through our stands,
how ’bout you pop out
another one of those cocky
one-liners before you die?
What’s the matter?
Catfish got
your tongue, brother?
( Yells )
Jotaro: So, what would you like
after i’m done with you?
Captain: Huh?
Jotaro: It would be a shame
to waste such fresh fish.
Fish paste?
Maybe a plate of sashimi?
I’ll make one hell of a meal
out of your stand.
Captain:
Don’t play games with me.
You’re trying to sound tough,
but I know the truth, boy.
The real terror of all this
is starting to sink in
to your thick skull.
I can even tell
what you’re thinking.
"How long can he
stay underwater?
"I can probably last
about two minutes,
but can he last
longer than me?"
Am I right, brother?
( Laughs ) Let me answer you.
My lung capacity is three times
that of a normal human’s.
( Jotaro gasps )
Captain: See, for years,
i’ve been training.
Six minutes and 12 seconds
is my best submerged time.
You must be dizzy just hearing
that number, right, brother?
And...
Dark blue moon’s fins
are cutters
that move faster
than a ship’s propeller,
far sharper, too.
Before you
get overconfident again,
you might wanna take
a good, hard look at your stand.
Seems dark blue moon’s barnacles
have taken a liking
to absorbing your stand’s power.
How does it feel
to have your life energy
slowly draining away
from your body?
( Chuckles )
Trying to run away
by swimming back up?
Take a good look around you.
( Laughs )
Haven’t you realized, brother,
dark blue moon has created
an underwater whirlpool?
There’s no way
you can possibly escape.
That’s right. Swim faster.
You’ll just make it
harder to breathe
while your power keeps draining.
But it’s little too early
to kill a stupid, smartass punk
like you just yet.
Joseph: It’s been too long!
He’s still not coming up!
Avdol: A giant whirlpool!
It must have him trapped.
Polnareff:
Where the hell is jojo?
Kakyoin: Let’s go and save him.
( Hierophant green grunts )
( Kakyoin groans )
These are scales.
That guy’s stand
has scales as sharp as razors.
Avdol: There are
countless scales
swirling in that whirlpool.
He wasn’t bluffing when he said
he could beat
all five of us at once.
It’s like a watery ant-lion pit.
If we dive in,
it’s very possible
we’ll be sliced to pieces.
( Star platinum yells )
Jotaro: His scales?
Captain: I’ll take another guess
at what you’re thinking.
"In a whirlpool,
only one spot stays still."
( Laughs )
Such mundane logic.
"It’s the eye.
If I jump into the center
where he is, I can attack him."
( Laughs )
That’s what you’re thinking,
right?
If you believe you can hit me
with that punch of yours again,
then come and give it a shot.
Throw your worthless stand
at me.
It’s power’s so drained,
it doesn’t have a chance.
See if you can manage an attack,
one that’s even sharper
than these underwater cutters.
I’m waiting, brother.
Avdol: Damn him!
We’re completely helpless.
Kakyoin: It’s jojo!
I just saw jojo
in the whirlpool.
( Polnareff speaking French )
I don’t think
he’s moving down there.
Joseph: So he went limp?
He wasn’t struggling
against the whirlpool?
Well, that might
actually be a good thing.
( Both gasp )
Captain: Weren’t you gonna
turn me into sashimi, boy?
You’re the one
who’s gonna be sliced up.
♪
Jotaro: Star finger!
Sorry. Did I interrupt you?
Who’s gonna be sashimi?
( Captain gurgling )
Jotaro: What’s that?
I can’t hear you.
You’re gonna have to speak up.
We’re underwater.
Captain: But your power
was being drained.
You let yourself go limp
on purpose, didn’t you?
You concentrated your power
in your fingers.
Th-that’s what you
were thinking all along.
Jotaro: Not even close
the only thing on my mind
is how gross it’ll be
when I kick your stupid ass
and you
piss yourself underwater,
and that’s all.
Bye, pops.
( Jotaro inhales )
Kakyoin: Jojo!
Joseph:
That’s my grandson for you.
Well done, jotaro.
- Hurry and come u--huh?
- ( Explosion )
Polnareff: Huh?
Th-that captain planted
some bombs after all! Damn it!
Joseph: Send out
a distress call!
( Men sighing )
Joseph: Here.
You should have some water
we’ve sent out distress calls,
so someone should be here
with a rescue ship soon enough.
Girl: Okay, just what
the hell is going on here?
I don’t get any of this.
Who are you guys?
Joseph: Just think of us
as fellow travelers.
You’re on a journey
to see your father,
while i’m on one
for my daughter.
Heh.
( Girl gasps )
Joseph: Hey, that’s
the only fresh water we have,
so don’t spit it out.
We need it.
Girl: N-n-no.
( Stammering )
Everyone, look there!
All: Hmm?
Joseph: Huh?
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian