♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Enyaba: Polnareff,
I shall savor killing you.
To avenge my dear son,
I shall rip out your insides
while you watch.
- Polnareff: Hey, madame!
- Enyaba: But I can’t let him
find hol horse’s body,
or else my chance will be lost.
Polnareff: She’s not
behind the counter, either.
Enyaba: It’ll be even worse
if the other three show up.
I need to kill them one by one,
damn it.
Stay back. Go away.
Polnareff: Oh, madame,
are you here?
I thought I heard some kind of
crash back here. Are you okay?
♪
Hmm.
I’m coming in, madame.
- ( Enyaba gasps, grunts )
- ( Thump )
( Chuckles )
Polnareff: Oh, no!
What happened?
Enyaba: Oh, it’s nothing.
It’s only a tiny fall.
Just bruised my hip
a little bit.
Polnareff: You fell down?
You can’t be falling now.
And you burned your left hand?
You’re being
much, much too careless.
Enyaba: Oh, thank you, dear boy.
I’m fine.
No problem. I promise.
Get out. Get out. Get out!
Who said you could
come in here, damn it?
♪
I’ll spare you my wrath for now,
but when the time is right,
i’ll kill you just like I killed
that bastard hol horse.
All it takes
is just a tiny, little wound,
and then you’re finished.
I’ll turn you into
my very own puppet of justice.
- Polnareff: Hmm?
- Enyaba: Eh?
Polnareff: Oh? Cool.
Here. Your staff.
Madame, you seem
to be sweating a lot.
Enyaba: It’s nothing.
Don’t concern yourself with me.
I’m fine.
Just go to your room,
and get some rest.
Polnareff: Well, if you insist.
So I was wondering,
are you running
the entire hotel
all by yourself?
Don’t you have some family
around to help, like a son?
( Enyaba gasping )
( Growls )
Polnareff: Huh? Sorry.
Did you say something?
Enyaba: Uh, I was just saying
i’ve gotten used
to living alone.
Polnareff: Ah, I see.
Sounds lonely to me.
I mean, didn’t your son
have a wife and kids?
Your grandkids could run around
and play in the lobby.
They’d definitely
cheer this place up.
It’d be a little noisy,
but that’s
what makes families great!
( Enyaba stammering )
Polnareff: If you had a son,
he’d probably
be older than me, right?
Hey, what’s the matter?
Did he move to the big city
or something?
( Enyaba groaning )
N-no. He passed away.
Polnareff: Oh, i’m so sorry.
That was
terribly insensitive of me.
Polnareff: You’re the one
who killed him, you monster.
I despise you.
I’ll slaughter you.
Polnareff: Please,
sit down and rest.
I’ll give you a nice back rub.
I know how it feels to be alone.
I lost my mom
when I was still just a kid.
Isn’t this great?
Ah, the memories.
Tonight, you can think
about me--( Laughs )--
as if i’m your own beloved son.
Ask me for anything, okay?
Enyaba: You rotten little brat.
I should just kill you
right now, you fool!
Polnareff: Wow,
you’re really tense.
I guess living alone
has been pretty tough on you.
- ( Hol horse groaning )
- ( Thump )
Polnareff: Hmm?
( Hol horse groaning )
( Enyaba gasps )
( Hol horse coughs )
Polnareff: Huh?
What’s that guy doing there?
Enyaba: Hol horse?
How is he still alive?
That miscreant must have
made his stand vanish
as soon as it shot the bullet
into his mouth.
Polnareff: What?
No! That face.
Hol horse: Hey.
Look behind you, polnareff.
Behind you, you fool!
Polnareff: No way!
You’re hol horse!
- ( Enyaba shrieks )
- Polnareff: What are you doing?
Enyaba: Getting my vengeance!
I’m the mother of centerfold,
who you mercilessly murdered
in cold blood!
- ( Polnareff gasps )
- ( Enyaba yelling )
Polnareff: Chariot!
So you were
a stand user all along!
Enyaba: Dare play a part
in murdering my boy,
and i’ll make sure
you’ll pay for it! ( Shrieks )
Polnareff: Mr. Joestar,
I need help!
Enyaba: Hah. It’s too late.
You won’t be calling
your trusty friends
anytime soon, my dear...
- ( Polnareff gasping )
- Enyaba: Because...
( Puppets moaning )
Enyaba: I’ve summoned
my own allies.
Polnareff: Who the hell
are you guys?
( Gasps )
Wait. It’s you.
B-but you’re dead.
You were dead when we got here.
You’re the one from India!
( Puppet moans )
Polnareff: Holy shit.
We’ve got zombies.
( Puppets moaning )
Enyaba: Behold the terrifying
power of justice, my stand.
I may have only one stand,
but justice, the fog stand,
can manipulate the dead,
increasing my power.
It can control
hundreds of corpses,
even thousands of them.
( Laughs )
Polnareff: Aren’t you taking
this grudge a bit too far?
To think that such a twisted
stand user was after us.
I had no idea.
Hol horse: This whole
godforsaken town’s
got it in for you.
And if you get
any kind of wound,
she’ll turn you into
her personal puppet.
Enyaba: I need only
to give you a little scratch.
It doesn’t take much, you know.
Soon you’ll be mine.
Then my stand, justice,
will take care of the rest.
You’re dead!
Get him!
Polnareff: I’m outta here!
Hol horse: Polnareff!
Don’t leave me here, please.
Polnareff: Oh, shut up.
Did you forget about stabbing
my friend avdol?
Now, why in the hell
should I save you?
You’re on your own, pal.
Enyaba: You can’t escape my
righteous vengeance, polnareff!
I’ll yank your brains out
through your nostrils!
I’ll snap your spine in half
and shatter your bones!
I’ll crush your balls
’til they pop!
My vengeance comes now!
- ( Laughing )
- ( Polnareff yelling )
She’s psychotic.
How can an old crone like her
possibly run so fast?
Enyaba: Take this.
Damn it. That filthy coward
ran into the back room.
After him, you fools!
Break down that door at once!
( Polnareff panting )
Merde. Just my luck.
This hallway leads
down to the basement.
I’m so far away from them now,
Mr. Joestar and the others
will never hear me.
I don’t think those
creepy zombies can beat me,
but if I get
even a single scratch,
i’ll be in trouble.
She’ll take control of me,
just like hol horse.
D-damn it.
Isn’t there any way outside?
- ( Thumping )
- ( Gasps )
These windows
have iron bars on them.
I can’t get out!
( Panting )
( Wood cracking )
Damn it!
I’ll hide in this room.
Oh, crap,
they broke down the door.
At this rate, i’m going
to have to fight them.
I just have to keep these freaks
as far away
from my skin as possible.
( Puppets moaning )
And now they’re
coming down the hallway.
They must be checking
every room.
Damn it. They’re getting
closer and closer.
Wait a minute. Oh, come on.
Did I run into another bathroom?
Why am I always
getting ambushed in bathrooms?
Damn it. The toilet is so dirty.
All right, just try it.
But the second you walk in,
my chariot will chop up the four
of you in a single breath.
( Footsteps receding )
Huh?
What’s going on?
Now it’s
totally quiet out there.
Creepy.
Damn zombies, that old hag,
what the hell are they doing?
Aren’t they going
to break down the door?
♪
What’s taking them so long?
Come on. Do something, damn it.
Hmm?
( Squelch )
( Yells )
( Enyaba laughs )
Polnareff: Ahh!
They were looking
through the keyhole
the whole time!
What the hell?
Merde! This is not good.
The bastard stabbed me
in the tongue!
( Yelling )
- ( Yelling continues )
- Enyaba: Perfect!
You’ve finally fallen
under my justice’s control,
you shitty little brat!
And now, if you
don’t open that door
and come out on your own
this second,
i’m going
to slowly crush your face
and pull you
through the keyhole!
Laugh now.
( Puppets laugh )
( Laughs )
How pitiful, polnareff.
Very pitiful, indeed.
( Laughs )
This isn’t even close
to the level of torture
you put my centerfold through.
Because of your cowardice,
my precious son died
in unimaginable agony.
Now, then, how about we have
you clean the bathroom, eh?
Sound like a plan to you?
( Polnareff groaning )
( Enyaba slurps )
Lick the toilet
until it sparkles like new.
Don’t be shy.
Lick it ’til it’s shiny,
like this.
( Babbling )
Polnareff: No, not that.
Anything but that.
( Grunting )
Oh, god, help me!
♪
( Door closes )
Enyaba: Oh, you startled me.
Is something the matter,
young man?
What can I do for you?
Jotaro: I’m here
looking for polnareff,
and I did knock.
Maybe you didn’t hear me,
because you were too busy
doing something else.
I wonder what.
( Enyaba gasps )
Jotaro: I’m looking
for polnareff,
but I can’t find him.
Seen him, grandma?
Enyaba: Damn. Now what?
Unlike polnareff,
this jotaro is clever
and knows the right questions
to ask to get what he wants.
I have to be careful
playing dumb will just
make him more suspicious.
I need something else.
What a troublesome brat.
I know. I’ll tell him
where he can find polnareff,
and as soon
as he turns his back,
i’ll turn him into
a pincushion with these.
Then he’ll be easy pickings
for my justice.
Yes, of course I can help you.
I know exactly where he is,
Mr. Jotaro.
He and I were
just having a lovely chat.
Jotaro: Oh?
( Polnareff grunting )
This isn’t good.
Jotaro has no idea
a tiny scratch
will spell his doom.
S-stay back.
Tell Mr. Joestar and kakyoin.
That hag is the enemy.
Enyaba: He’s in the bathroom,
but he’s been in there
for quite some time.
( Chuckles )
Jotaro: Of course
he’s taking a shit.
Through this door here?
Enyaba: Yes, that’s right.
Once you’re through the door,
make a left turn.
The bathroom is
at the very end of the hall.
What an incompetent fool.
You are a child after all.
Murdering polnareff
will delight my son’s soul,
and spilling your blood, jotaro,
will send lord dio
in Egypt into jubilation.
Jotaro: Oh, yeah. I forgot.
You have a second?
I got a question.
- ( Enyaba grunts )
- ( Slice )
Jotaro: Huh? What’s the matter?
Did you trip,
or are you just that clumsy?
You should be more careful.
Enyaba: That was too close.
Jotaro: Yeah.
Could have been real bad.
It could have gone into your eye
or cut a huge chunk
out of your scrawny neck.
You’re pretty damn lucky.
Sorry to ask
before you even get up,
but I have a few more questions.
First on the list, how did
you know my name is jotaro?
I never told you my name.
No one has,
not since we got here.
Enyaba: Huh?
Jotaro: I find that strange.
Well? Come on, tell me.
You know, it’s funny.
Maybe it’s because I
watched "Columbo" as a kid,
but it’s little details like
that that keep me up at night.
Enyaba: Oh, you’re beginning to
hurt this old lady’s feelings.
( Coughs ) It’s the guest book.
You wrote your name
in the guest book earlier.
Don’t tell me
you don’t remember.
( Coughs )
It’s so dry.
You wrote "jotaro kujo," yes.
Oh, then I guess you mean...
This guest book here?
Enyaba: Yes. That’s it.
See? Your name is right here.
( Gasps )
"Qtaro kujo"?
Jotaro: "Jotaro" isn’t written
anywhere in this old thing.
Calling me joestar when we first
met was your first mistake.
I’ve suspected you since.
I told the others
not to use my name,
and yet, you know it,
which could only mean...
( Enyaba gasping )
Jotaro: Cut the crap,
you old hag.
I already know you’re one of
the stand users that’s after us.
The jig is up.
( Enyaba growling )
Jotaro: What’s the matter now?
Aren’t you going to show me
your stand and fight?
Enyaba: You’re looking
right at it.
( Puppets groaning )
( Star platinum yelling )
♪
( Enyaba gasping )
( Laughs )
( Jotaro gasps )
Enyaba: My stand, justice,
always prevails.
All it needs
is one small scratch,
and then your life
is as good as forfeit.
You’ve fallen
into my trap, jotaro.
( Polnareff grunting )
Jotaro: Polnareff.
Hol horse: Jotaro, it’s me,
hol horse, remember?
Enyaba’s stand is made
entirely out of fog.
It’ll split
your wound right open
and start flowing
through your body.
That’s how
she controls you with it.
It’ll even control corpses.
Enyaba: Shut your mouth,
hol horse!
Star platinum: Ora!
( Yelling )
( Enyaba laughs )
Can you punch the fog
with your fist
or cut the fog with your sword
or shoot it with a gun?
I don’t think so.
Absolutely futile. ( Laughs )
There’s nothing you can do
but accept your fate.
Hol horse:
It’s the biggest, toughest,
fiercest stand there is.
Ours are puny by comparison.
We’re no match for it.
Nothing stands a chance
against justice.
Enyaba: Lovely.
Keep it coming, hol horse.
Your fearful praise
is music to my ears.
( Laughs )
Now i’ll control you,
too, jotaro.
Polnareff: Quick,
run away, jotaro.
She’s gonna turn you
into a puppet!
Jotaro: Good grief.
I don’t need to run.
Before that old hag
takes another breath,
i’ll defeat that stand
and send her packing.
Enyaba: Huh? What was that?
I could have sworn you just
made some idiotic proclamation
about defeating me,
you little brat.
Before I take another breath,
is that right?
Well, i’ll do that--
( gasping )
I’ll do that right--
What did you do to me?
- Polnareff: Huh?
- ( Hol horse gasps )
Polnareff:
Jotaro’s star platinum
is sucking in her entire stand!
Enyaba: No, no, please stop.
( Gasps ) I can’t breathe.
Polnareff:
And he’s holding it in!
He’s suffocating that bitch.
( Enyaba gasping )
♪
Jotaro: Huh. You see that?
Looks like her head
is in a bit of a fog.
You ask me,
that’s justice at its finest.
Enyaba: I’m so angry.
( Gags )
( Polnareff coughs )
What do you mean,
"what have I been licking?"
You ask such stupid questions.
I honestly don’t see
why that matters.
( Coughs )
The toilet.
Joseph: Eh?
You were licking what, again?
I couldn’t hear you very well.
Polnareff:
Who cares what it was?
Now I need to disinfect
my tongue, okay?
Give me the medicine already.
Kakyoin: Hmm? I thought
I just heard the word "toilet."
( Joseph giggling )
Kakyoin: What are you
giggling about?
Joseph: Actually,
I already knew about that,
but I couldn’t resist
picking on him about this first.
- ( Giggles )
- Polnareff: Hold on!
Jotaro already told you
what happened, didn’t he?!
You shitty old man!
You were just messing with me!
Forget the medicine.
Joseph: All right, all right.
I’m sorry,
come here,
and i’ll fix you up, polnareff.
If you don’t take care of that,
it’ll get infected.
Ahem.
Toilet.
You licked it real good.
( Polnareff whimpers )
( Joseph laughing )
Polnareff: Jotaro,
kakyoin, come on.
Let’s just get the hell
out of here.
Jotaro: Everyone, come outside.
- Kakyoin: Eh?
- Joseph: Huh?
Hmm?
♪
What on earth?
We step outside of the hotel,
and this place is a...
Kakyoin: It’s a graveyard.
She was using her stand’s fog
to make this graveyard
look like a town and a hotel.
Polnareff: So the whole time
we were here,
we were talking
to some corpses six feet under?
Polnareff: You wanna
take her with us?
Are you serious?!
Jotaro: Sure am.
We need to know
how many more stand users
are out there,
what their powers are,
and wherever dio’s dug a hole
for himself in Egypt,
as well as what his power is.
Joseph: If we get
the hag to tell us,
it might finally give us
the edge that we need.
That’s worth the risk
of dragging her around.
( Polnareff gulps )
Kakyoin: I highly doubt
she’ll be willing
to share
that information, though.
Joseph: We just need to use
my hermit purple.
I’ll project everything
she’s thinking onto a TV screen.
Polnareff: Great idea!
We’ll hop over to the next town
and use a TV there.
( Car engine starts )
Hmm? ( Yells )
Hol horse, you slimeball!
Kakyoin: That’s our car!
Hol horse: Sorry, boys.
I’m stickin’ with dio after all.
Catch you all later,
provided you all don’t die
before then, that is!
A little advice for y’all--
you better put a bullet between
that old lady’s eyes real soon,
or else you’ll find out just
how terrifying dio really is,
and you do not want that.
Polnareff: Hmm?
Hol horse: See ya!
Polnareff: Does anyone know
what he’s talking about?
’cause I don’t.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian