♪
Woman: Ah, my,
that looks quite good on you.
In all my years,
i’ve never received such
a strange request for clothing,
but the pleasure was mine, sir.
Jotaro: Here. I gotta go.
Keep the change.
See ya.
Woman: Uh, thank you, sir.
( Anne squeals ) Let go!
Let go of me! And don’t you
dare touch me there, you jerk!
Polnareff: Hey,
don’t say it like that.
- Kakyoin: Here’s her ticket.
- Anne: No! I don’t wanna!
I wanna keep going
with you guys! Eh?
Joseph: Listen, little miss.
We’re not vacationing here.
My daughter, jotaro’s mother,
is in grave danger
at the moment.
( Anne gasps )
Joseph: We’re on this journey
to save my daughter’s life,
not to put yours at risk.
Forget this
running-away business,
and start heading home.
I’m sure your parents
are worried sick
wondering where you are.
Polnareff: There.
Anne: Fine. I suppose so.
I’ll make you look good
this time, grandpa.
Huh?
Joseph: Hmm? What’s the matter?
( Anne grunts ) Nothing.
See ya! Life is just
a bunch of goodbyes anyway.
I do sort of wish
I could have seen him once more
before I had to go.
Huh?
( Laughs )
♪
Goodbye, jojo!
You better save your mom!
We’re all counting on you!
I’ll be cheering you on!
Jotaro: Hmph.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Pakistan
is a young country,
established in 1947 following
its separation from India.
But when Japan was still
a hunter-gatherer culture,
Pakistan was the seat of
a highly-developed civilization.
Here in Pakistan,
the people carry on
the 5,000-year history
of the Indian subcontinent.
Joseph: I gotta say, jotaro,
i’m impressed you got
a Japanese school uniform
made here in Pakistan.
The fit is perfect, too.
Jotaro: It’s 100% wool.
Kakyoin: Hey, polnareff,
are you okay driving right now?
The fog in this area
is getting quite thick.
Polnareff: These aren’t exactly
the safest conditions.
It’s one hell of a drop
off the right side,
and there’s
no guardrail anywhere.
Joseph: Hmm. The fog looks
even thicker up ahead.
It’s not even 3:00 yet,
but we should head in.
Let’s find a place to stay
in that town for the night.
Polnareff: Do you think
they have nice hotels?
Kakyoin: A nice hotel, huh?
Polnareff: That’s right,
and it’d better have
a decent bathroom.
I--i just couldn’t get used
to the really strange toilets
they have all over India
and the middle east.
( Jotaro gasps )
What the hell?
Was that a dead dog?
Joseph:
What’s the matter, jotaro?
Jotaro: Hmm?
Oh. Uh, it was nothing.
Joseph: Hmm?
Hey, this is a nice little town,
don’t you think?
There must be at least
a few thousand people
living here. Eh?
Kakyoin: Let’s ask about a hotel
at that restaurant over there.
Polnareff: But there’s
a weird quiet about this place.
No matter where we’ve gone,
every other place
has been rowdy and congested.
Joseph: It’s probably
because of the fog.
Listen up, guys.
In Pakistan and the rest
of the islamic world,
this is how you greet people.
First, you smile and say...
"As-salaam alaikum."
♪
Eh...
( Gasps )
( Grunts )
Uh, no harm intended.
( Chuckles )
No need to close up shop
just for us, sir.
We just wanted
to ask a question.
Are there any hotels
here in town?
♪
Uh...
Anybody home?
Man: I do not know.
- Joseph: Huh?
- Man: Good day.
Joseph: Hey, wait a minute!
What do you mean,
you don’t know? Huh?
( Gasps )
Huh? What’s with that guy?
That can’t be right.
I must have imagined it.
Polnareff: I’m sure
he couldn’t understand you,
because
your pronunciation’s so bad.
Let’s just go ask
that guy over there.
Excuse me. Sorry,
but we’re looking
for a hotel around here,
preferably a hotel
with nice, clean bathrooms.
Do you know any that--
( gasps )
♪
Whoa! Hey, you, what’s wrong?!
All: What the hell?!
Polnareff: He’s dead!
With that look of fear
on his face.
Wh-what’s going on?
Why is he
lying dead in the road?
What could have killed him,
a heart attack?
A stroke?
Jotaro: It’s possible, but look.
What we’ve got here
is no ordinary heart failure.
Polnareff: Huh?
( Gasps ) It’s a gun.
Wait a minute.
This guy’s holding a gun!
Kakyoin: You just noticed?
Jotaro: Check it out.
It’s still smoking.
Joseph: He must have
just fired it,
maybe two to five minutes ago.
Either way, he must have died
right before
we arrived in town.
Polnareff: Do you think
he shot himself?
Kakyoin: No, I doubt it.
His body doesn’t seem
to have any visible wounds,
and there’s no blood anywhere.
Polnareff:
Then how’d this guy die?
This isn’t natural. Look at him!
His face is all twisted, like he
was screaming in utter terror!
Joseph: Astounding.
You gotta wonder who or what
he shot at with that gun.
What exactly happened?
Kakyoin: Didn’t anyone here
see anything?
No one’s stopped to help.
Excuse me! Ma’am, wait!
Someone has died here!
Please call the police!
♪
( Gasps )
Woman: Pardon me, young man.
My boils
seem to be festering today.
My apologies.
You had a question.
What was it that you needed?
( Kakyoin gasps )
I asked if you could
please call the police, ma’am.
Woman: The police?
What would I do that for?
Kakyoin: Look!
That man’s dead.
Woman: Hmm.
Someone is dead, you say?
How terribly unfortunate.
I’m not sure if there is
anything I can do about that.
Kakyoin: I already asked you
to call the police twice.
Woman: Of course.
Call the police.
I think you did say that.
Well, good day, sir.
My boils are infected.
They are so itchy,
so terribly itchy.
( Kakyoin gags )
( Gasping )
What is with the people
in this town?
There’s a man
lying dead in the street,
and nobody seems even
the slightest bit concerned.
( Bird squawks )
Didn’t they hear the gunshot?
Nobody’s doing anything.
It’s like they don’t even care.
These people are more oblivious
than the most jaded new yorker
or tokyoite.
Jotaro: That dog...
Polnareff: This blasted fog
just keeps getting
thicker and thicker.
Kakyoin: It’s almost
as if the fog
is swallowing the town whole.
Polnareff:
This is really creepy.
Call me crazy,
but doesn’t that part there
look like a skull?
( Skull laughs )
Jotaro: What do you want to do?
You don’t think
it could be the work
of another stand user, do you?
Joseph: Eh, probably not.
There’s no motive.
Why would someone
who’s after us kill a man
who has nothing to do with us
before we even got here?
There’s no reason
for a stand user to kill him.
Jotaro: Who knows?
The way he died
is obviously unnatural.
Let’s examine the body
before the police come.
Just try not to touch it.
Joseph: Right.
This might be something.
It appears he was traveling,
too, just like us.
He has bus and train tickets
in his pocket.
And he looks like
he might be Indian.
He’s carrying
Indian money on him.
I’m guessing
he’s not from this town.
Oh?
♪
Look at this wound.
He’s got a gaping hole here,
right in his upper chest.
This must be what killed him.
Jotaro: Hang on. Why isn’t
there any blood coming out?
With a fatal chest wound
this big,
there should be blood
gushing everywhere.
Unless, of course...
This is no ordinary murder.
Looks like things
are about to get messy.
We’ve gotta
get to the bottom of this.
It’s time to search him.
Take off his clothes.
( All gasp )
Polnareff:
What happened to his body?!
There are tons of holes
all over this guy!
He’s like that cartoon cheese
you see on "Tom and Jerry"!
Joseph: And there’s
not a drop of blood
anywhere near those wounds.
How on earth
was this man killed?
What does all of this mean?
Jotaro: Be careful.
If there wasn’t
a stand user here before,
you can bet
there’s one here now.
Joseph: Everyone,
get in the car!
We’re leaving this town now!
( Yells ) What the--
all: Hmm?
Joseph: Impossible!
This isn’t the car!
Oh, no!
( Yells ) Hermit purple!
( Grunting )
( Yells )
Jotaro: Hey, old man...
What in the hell are you doing?
You’re crazy.
( Joseph sighs )
Huh? Oh, no!
What do you mean,
what am I doing?
The car was right here
just minute ago.
Polnareff: Huh?
What are you talking about?
We just parked the car
over there and walked.
Joseph: What?!
But just now,
I could have sworn that--
( gasps )
♪
( Staff tapping )
( Men grunting )
Enyaba: Well, hello, good sirs.
I see you are travelers.
I’m afraid, with this fog,
it’s dangerous
to leave the town now.
There are many cliffs, you know.
I run my own bed-and-breakfast
not far from here.
If you’d like, why not
stay there for the night?
There’s plenty of room
for everyone.
I’ll even give you
a healthy discount.
Polnareff: Finally.
We’ve actually met
a normal person for once.
( Enyaba chuckles )
♪
Kakyoin: We have to assume
a stand user
is hiding
somewhere in this town.
With this fog, there’s no
telling what our enemy could do.
They could be next to us,
and we wouldn’t know.
We absolutely cannot
let our guard down tonight.
Polnareff: You know, guys,
I realize no one’s
attacked us quite yet,
but, damn, this town is creepy.
( Staff echoes )
Enyaba: Come on.
This way, master joestar.
That building over there
is my bed-and-breakfast.
Follow me, and i’ll
show you to your rooms.
Try not to fall behind.
( Men grumble )
Enyaba: I know
it doesn’t look like much,
but it has history.
About 20 years ago, one of
the 007 movies was filmed here,
and when John Lennon of
the Beatles visited the country,
he spent the entire time
in our little hotel.
Polnareff: What?! Seriously?!
Enyaba: Oh, no,
I was just pulling
your leg, young man.
Polnareff: Wha--
enyaba: Still,
it is quite a lovely hotel.
I’ve put my heart
and soul into it.
We don’t have
any other guests at the moment,
so you can pick the dinner menu.
Would you prefer meat?
If not,
we have fresh fish available.
Jotaro: Wait a second, grandma.
Before, you called me "joestar,"
didn’t you?
( Enyaba gasps )
Jotaro: How did you
know my name?
Joseph: Hmm?
( Enyaba stammering )
Uh...
Come, now. That delightful
young man next to you
said, "Mr. Joestar," earlier.
I may be old,
but my ears still work.
Polnareff: You mean me?
I think I said it,
but i’m not sure.
Enyaba: Ah, you did, sir.
When you’ve been working
in this business
for as many years as I have,
you really learn to memorize
people’s names quickly.
- ( Laughs ) So i’m sure of it.
- ( Jotaro grunts )
Polnareff: By the way, ma’am,
I just noticed the bandages.
What happened to your hand?
Enyaba: Uh, oh, this?
A minor burn, nothing more.
I suppose it’s just my old age,
but I accidentally spilled
boiling water on it.
( Chuckles )
Polnareff: Oh,
don’t be silly, madame.
You hardly look a day over 40,
and that’s god’s honest truth.
What do say you and I
get dinner alone? ( Chuckles )
( Enyaba laughs )
Oh, you naughty boy.
Don’t tease an old woman
like that. ( Chuckles )
( Both laughing )
Enyaba: You damn
babbling, pathetic fool.
It is you I despise most,
polnareff.
I’ll make you suffer a pain
one thousand times worse
than what my son endured.
Then i’ll cut off your dick
and rip out your guts
to finish you off.
Joseph: Oh, this doesn’t
look bad at all.
Polnareff: Here, kakyoin.
Kakyoin: Right.
Polnareff: My autograph’s
worth as much as lennon’s.
Kakyoin: Here.
Polnareff:
I’m Paul-nareff, after all.
Make sure you take care of it.
Enyaba: Of course.
I’ll make sure
it’s preserved for all time.
To commemorate
the day I murder you.
Jotaro: It’s done.
Enyaba: Well, then, allow me
to show you
to your rooms, gentlemen.
( Footsteps echoing )
( Polnareff grunts )
( Sighs )
Man, talk about a weird town.
Now, time to hit the loo.
( Static hissing )
Kakyoin: I don’t think
it’s functional.
Joseph: Oh. If that’s the case,
I won’t be able
to use hermit purple
- to get info on the enemy.
- ( Door opens )
- Polnareff: Hey, Mr. Joestar.
- Joseph: What’s the matter?
Polnareff: Looks like my room
doesn’t have a bathroom.
Is there one in here I can use?
Kakyoin: Perhaps
the bathroom here is communal.
Polnareff: Ah. Of course.
( Kakyoin sighs )
Joseph: He’s so carefree.
Good grief.
A stand user
could attack at any moment.
He should be on guard.
♪
( Footsteps echoing )
( Spurs jingle )
( Bell rings )
( Enyaba gasps )
Hol horse: So the joestar party
is on the third floor?
Maybe me and my six-shooter
ought to pay them a visit.
Enyaba: Ah, hol horse.
So you’ve come.
Hol horse: That’s right.
I finally managed
to track those sorry bastards
as far as this creepy town,
but finding you
is a surprise, enyaba.
I didn’t think you’d come
all the way out here yourself.
( Enyaba chuckles )
( Sobbing )
Hol horse:
What’s the matter, enyaba?
Did I say something wrong?
( Enyaba crying )
Forgive me.
I’m just happy, hol horse.
It means so much
that you’re here.
Thank you for coming to see
this lonely old woman.
It is so wonderful
to finally see you.
- ( Crying )
- Hol horse: Huh?
Enyaba: Tell me something.
You and my son were friends,
were you not, hol horse?
Hol horse: Were we friends?
Uh, well, i--( Coughs )
Yes, we were
as thick as thieves, ma’am.
( Enyaba sobs )
So you were close?
Hol horse: Yeah, we were
practically brothers.
He was a dear friend
and an excellent partner.
What’s this all about?
You aren’t acting
like yourself at all, enyaba.
( Enyaba murmurs )
His death must weigh
heavily on you.
Will you avenge him?
Is that why you’re here?
Hol horse: Yes!
That’s exactly it!
I’m gonna make sure
those bastards pay
for killing my best friend.
( Enyaba chuckles )
( Hol horse gasps )
Enyaba: That’s exactly
what I want to hear!
( Hol horse screams )
( Enyaba yells )
Because now I can kill you,
too, you filthy traitor!
( Hol horse screams )
Enyaba,
what the hell are you doing?!
( Screaming )
Enyaba: Idiot. Isn’t it obvious?
You abandoned him
to save yourself.
I swore I would kill you
the moment I saw you again.
You deserve
the same as the joestars.
How dare you call yourself
his best friend?
Cretin! Judas!
Hol horse: Wait!
You got it all wrong.
By the time I got there,
centerfold was
already a goner, honest.
- ( Enyaba screams )
- ( Hol horse gasps )
( Enyaba growls ) You wretch.
You’re as unforgivable
as that bastard, polnareff.
I’ll have you die at the hands
of my stand, justice.
Hol horse: Wait. Have mercy!
♪
Enyaba: Only a few have seen
the terrifying power
of my stand,
and now you will join
all of them in death, hol horse.
( Hol horse gasping )
Huh? What the hell is happening
to the blood in my arm?!
It’s like
it’s all just evaporating.
( Groans )
( Screaming )
Enyaba: It made
such a fine wound, did it not?
That’s right. This is justice,
a stand that’s made of fog.
Any wound
my stand happens to graze
becomes a gaping hole,
and then...
( Justice laughing )
Enyaba: Justice wants to dance,
hol horse.
My stand’s fog has entered
your arm, like a string,
and now you’re a helpless puppet
I can do with as I please.
You will die by your own hand,
hol horse!
( Hol horse muttering )
( Groans )
( Enyaba cackles )
Hol horse: Damn it.
You shouldn’t get so damn cocky.
Emperor!
Die, you crazy old hag!
( Gasps )
Enyaba: Justice prevails.
- ( Gunshot )
- ( Crash )
Polnareff: Huh?
What the hell was that noise?
Sounded like an giant explosion.
It came from the room
at the back
of the downstairs lobby.
♪
( Enyaba chuckles )
( Gasps )
Joseph: Is something wrong,
polnareff?
Polnareff: Huh?
Kakyoin: We heard
something strange
and came to investigate.
Polnareff: Same here.
I was about to check downstairs.
I’ll look in the lobby first.
Call me if you
find anything, okay?
Jotaro: Hmm.
♪
Enyaba: Your time’s
finally come, polnareff.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian