♪
Dio: Enyaba, there’s something
i’d like to ask you.
What does it mean to live?
Enyaba: It’s to obtain
all that one desires.
If you were to distill life
into its essence,
that is what it would be.
A lust for riches,
a desire for fame,
food, love, and lovers,
that is life’s goal.
( Chuckles )
Dio: But one must always fight
to get what one wants.
Isn’t that correct, enyaba?
Enyaba: Indeed. ( Chuckles )
Dio: And if the battle is lost
and one fails to obtain
what one desires most,
the result is frustration,
pain, and a sense of failure.
One carries the wound
into the future,
into the next fearful battle.
I believe conquering that fear
once and for all
is what it means to live.
The one who stands
at the pinnacle
is the one who has no fear.
Do you understand, enyaba?
Enyaba: I was
the one who told you
about the existence
of your stand
and how to use it.
Also you have an immortal body.
Is there anything
you could possibly fear?
Dio: Perhaps, old woman.
Enyaba: Hmm.
What burdens you, my lord?
Dio: The joestar bloodline.
Enyaba: Hmm? Joestar?
They worry you?
Those worms are mere trash.
Your enemies
are no match for your stand.
Dio: Yes, but I must
believe it’s destiny
when the lives of those worms
are so thoroughly entangled
with mine.
It is a fate that has
been written for us all
from the very beginning.
Let me be clear.
It is not the joestars
that I fear,
but the fact that I can never
underestimate their bloodline.
In order to obliterate all fear,
I have decided
that I must remove the joestars
from the cogs of fate.
Enyaba: You want to go
and eliminate them yourself,
simply because you feel that
they cannot be underestimated?
Dio: Yes.
Enyaba: Foolishness!
You should never engage
in such trivial matters!
They are beneath
someone of your stature!
I have sent seven stand users
to command--
the empress,
the wheel of fortune,
the hanged man and temperance,
the emperor, and the devil--
all of them on the move
and ready to strike
whenever you call.
Thanks to these allies,
you need not take
any action yourself, lord dio.
( Cackling )
( Joseph gasps )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Men gasping )
Sailor: A freighter.
Sailor #2:
I didn’t see it at all.
( Jotaro groans )
Joseph: Jotaro, something’s
bothering you, isn’t it?
Are you worried there might be
another stand user
on this freighter?
It’s not ideal,
but we could handle it.
Jotaro: Not quite.
Strange they lowered the stairs,
but there’s not a single soul
to be seen around here anywhere.
Joseph: Eh?
♪
Polnareff: This ship came
all this way to rescue us.
There has to be
some sort of crew onboard.
Even if they’re all stand users,
i’m getting on this boat.
I’m done drifting in circles.
( Men grunt )
Joseph: Hmm?
Jotaro: Take my hand, kid.
I’ll help you get up.
Girl: Um...
Blehh!
Jotaro: Good grief.
( Ship creaking )
♪
( No audible dialogue )
( Creaking continues )
Joseph: Hey,
what’s with this ship?
There’s no captain
in the control room,
there’s no engineer
in the radio room.
There’s no one anywhere.
And yet, look at this.
All the gauges and machinery
are working properly,
just like normal.
Polnareff: Maybe they’re
just all in the bathroom
with a bad case of the runs.
Joseph: Hey!
Isn’t anyone around?!
Girl: You have to see this.
Come here! Quick!
- Polnareff: Hmm?
- Joseph: Eh?
Girl: An ape.
There’s an ape inside that cage.
( Orangutan grunts )
Kakyoin: It’s an orangutan.
Joseph: Who the hell cares
about a friggin’ ape?!
Let’s split up
and find whoever’s
been feeding this thing.
♪
( Girl gasps )
( Orangutan sighs )
Avdol: Well?
Sailor #3: Hmm.
It doesn’t appear
to be broken, but...
Joseph: Uh...
Eh?
Avdol!
That sailor! Watch out!
( All yell )
( Girl screams )
Jotaro: Oh, good grief.
That isn’t any way
to greet a lady you’ve
never met before, now, is it?
( Sailors gasping )
Sailor #3: But no one
was touching the controls.
Sailor #2:
I saw that crane move,
even though there was
no one operating it.
I don’t believe in ghosts,
but what the hell?
Sailor #3: I saw it, too.
That crane impaled him
all on its own.
Joseph: Keep your guard up.
There’s someone hostile here.
Hey, don’t touch the machinery.
You got that?
If it moves
or runs on electricity,
don’t lay a finger on it.
If you want to live,
then you’ll do exactly
as I tell you. Understand?
Get into the cabin below,
and stay there
until I tell you otherwise.
( Sailors murmuring )
Joseph: Did any one of you see
even a glimpse of a stand
just now?
- Polnareff: I didn’t.
- Avdol: My apologies.
I was the closest to the crane,
and yet I felt nothing.
I should have been able
to sense something.
Kakyoin: All right.
I’ll send hierophant green
to take a look around the ship.
♪
Girl: I have no idea
what’s going on,
but scary things keep happening
whenever you guys are around.
Could you guys be jinxed?
I’ve heard about people
who cause disasters
that endanger everyone.
If that’s what you are,
i’d better stay away.
( Gasps )
Joseph: I have
just one bit of truth for you,
so listen closely.
Whatever happens,
we’re on your side.
Girl: Uh...Huh.
Joseph: Stay safe.
Make sure you stay
with the others. Got it?
Girl: Mm-hmm.
♪
( Orangutan grunts )
( Grunting )
( Sighs )
( Grunts )
Girl: Do you want me
to open the cage for you?
But I can’t.
I have no idea where the key is,
and you’re too big to let out.
You’re giving me an apple?
But it doesn’t make any sense.
This apple’s
been cut with a knife,
and the color
hasn’t really changed yet.
It looks totally fresh,
like it was cut a second ago,
so I guess there really must be
someone hiding
somewhere on this boat.
Where is the person
who feeds you?
Has he gone off
and left you here?
- ( Wood flicks )
- Huh?
Orangutan: Mmm.
Girl: Whoa.
You’re a pretty smart monkey.
Who trained you to do that?
( Orangutan blows )
( Grunting )
( Girl gasps ) No way.
A monkey like you is
actually into looking at...
( Swallows ) Pinups of girls?
( Orangutan sighing )
Sailor #3: Hey, kid,
be careful there.
( Girl gasps )
Sailor #2: They say an orangutan
has five times the strength
of a normal human,
so it could
easily rip off your arm.
Sailor #3: Come on. Stay with us
in the room on the other side.
Don’t go off by yourself.
Girl: Oh, okay.
( Orangutan grunting )
♪
Kakyoin: It’s inconceivable.
I’ve had hierophant green
search every inch of this ship,
but I can’t find a single sign
of human life aboard.
We’ve searched
every pipe and crevice,
but still came up empty-handed.
( Jotaro sighs )
Sailor #3: Anything?
Sailor #4: It’s no use.
I can’t get a connection.
Sailor #3:
Well, try again, damn it.
( Girl sniffing )
Ehh, gross.
I feel sticky
from the salt water.
( Groans )
Huh? Hmm.
( Handle creaks )
( Gasps )
( Humming a tune )
( Screen clatters )
( Continues humming )
( Giggles )
♪
( Sighs )
Huh? ( Gasps )
( Orangutan grunts )
( Girl whimpering )
♪
( Orangutan grunting )
( Girl gasping )
( Orangutan sighing )
( Girl whimpering )
( Orangutan grunts )
( Sniffing )
- ( Roaring )
- ( Girl screaming )
Jotaro: Hey.
( Orangutan groans )
Girl: Jojo!
Jotaro: Take your lock,
you stinking ape.
Seems that this ape...
Isn’t your
run-of-the-mill monkey.
Could it be that he’s the one?
Star platinum: Ora!
( Orangutan laughs )
Jotaro: Wait.
Who the hell
ripped out that fan?
Had to be him.
So this ape’s a stand user,
but where’s the stand?
I should be able to see
the damn thing, but I can’t.
Doesn’t make any sense.
What the--
the steel propeller
bent on its own,
like it’s alive.
- ( Orangutan roars )
- Girl: Jojo.
Jotaro: Hey,
what’s going on here?
( Orangutan growls )
( Roars )
Jotaro: Son of a bitch.
There’s no stand in sight,
and somehow the window broke?
Star platinum!
( Star platinum yells )
( Orangutan grunting )
Jotaro: What’s with this thing?
The ape just sank into the wall
and disappeared.
Hey, you saw that, right?
Stay close to me.
Something bad is going down.
The ape vanished into the wall,
but that orangutan
has to be the stand user.
When I touched it earlier,
I felt a stand’s energy
coming from it.
I have no doubt that he’s
the one we’re looking for.
Doesn’t make any sense.
Why can’t I see the stand,
like I always do?
( Gasps )
Wait.
What if i’m seeing it already?
- ( Rumbling )
- ( Both gasp )
Girl: What’s happening?
( Men gasping )
Avdol: Whoa. What’s going on?
Joseph: This isn’t good.
Polnareff: It’s swallowing us.
Joseph: Is the freighter
trying to--
is it possible
the ship itself is--
jotaro: So the stand
is actually the freighter.
( Orangutan laughs )
Jotaro: Damn. You son of a...
Joseph: All of it,
this ship itself
and everything on it,
is a gigantic stand!
Polnareff: The entire ship?
So there are stands
that non-stand users,
like that girl
and the crew members, can see?
Avdol: The only possible
explanation for that
is that its immense energy
is making it possible
to be seen with the naked eye.
But all this must demand
a tremendous amount of energy
to operate a stand
as huge as this.
Kakyoin,
send hierophant green to jotaro.
He can help get us out of this.
Kakyoin: I...Can’t do that.
It’s got a firm hold
on my stand, and i’m stuck.
Polnareff: This is
what it means to face death.
We fell for this trap, and
now we’re hopelessly ensnared
with no way to escape.
( Kakyoin gasps )
The pressure keeps increasing.
At this rate, our bodies
are going to be pulverized.
We...will be...
Joseph: Damn. We were careless.
We’ve got to--( Groans )
( Orangutan grunting )
Narrator: The word that
the orangutan was pointing to
was "strength."
It means force, energy,
power, or aid,
and it is the eighth card
of the tarot deck.
It suggests challenge,
a strong will,
and hidden powers.
( Orangutan grunting )
( Star platinum grunts )
( Orangutan gasps )
( Chuckling )
Jotaro: Damn ape.
Thinks he’s won already, huh?
Narrator: "This entire ship
is my stand, and you’ve lost.
"You’re totally outmatched
and helpless,
and there’s
nothing you can do."
( Orangutan hooting )
Narrator: Jotaro needed
no explanation.
He knew exactly
what the ape was saying.
( Orangutan grunts )
( Girl whimpers )
♪
- ( Orangutan grunts )
- ( Girl yelps )
( Orangutan growls )
( Growls )
Jotaro: Over here, monkey.
That button’s
not part of your stand.
( Orangutan growls )
( Jotaro scoffs ) Are you angry?
I guess it wounded your pride,
since you thought
you’d already beaten us.
No, it’s not hurt at all, is it?
Because apes like you
don’t have any pride.
( Orangutan roars )
Jotaro: That’s exactly what
makes you an ape and not a man.
Star platinum:
What’s going to hurt now...
Is your head!
( Orangutan screaming )
Jotaro: Good grief.
( Orangutan yelps )
( Grunting )
Jotaro: I’ve heard that,
when frightened,
animals show their stomachs
to signal their submission
to the enemy.
So you’re asking me
to forgive you?
( Orangutan grunting )
Jotaro: I’m afraid your actions
have already gone
beyond the rules of the jungle,
so I don’t think so.
( Star platinum yelling )
Ora!
( Girl yelps )
What the--
the pipes and walls
are distorting.
The whole ship is twisting up.
Jotaro: Hey,
be surprised about it later.
- This ship is about to sink.
- ( Girl gasps )
Jotaro: It’s time to leave.
Get back to the lifeboats.
♪
Girl: Wow, I can’t believe it.
The ship’s shape is changing.
It’s turning into
a shabby little boat.
Avdol: If I hadn’t seen it
myself, I wouldn’t believe it.
That ape was traveling the sea
on his own stand.
What terrifying power.
That was the first time
i’ve encountered such energy.
Joseph: Hate to say it,
but we were completely
overwhelmed this round.
If jotaro hadn’t figured it out,
we would have been done for.
Are we going to encounter
even more stands
with crazy, unknown powers
from now on?
We’ll have to be ready
for anything.
Polnareff: Hey,
you want some gum?
Avdol: So we’re going
to be drifting again.
Jotaro: Good grief.
My cigarettes are soaked.
Polnareff:
There’ll be plenty of sun
and time for them
to get dry, jojo.
Joseph: We’ll have to pray
that we get rescued
and reach Singapore
safely and soon.
Kakyoin: It’s been four days
since we left Japan.
Narrator: There are 46 days
until time runs out
for the joestars.
Enyaba: My lord, it would appear
that strength has been defeated.
But have no fear.
The remaining six stand users
are all very powerful
and each deadlier than the last,
and one of them is my son.
His right arm
shall crush our enemies.
The joestars
will not pose a threat
when he’s finished with them.
( Laughs )
( Dio chuckles )
You are a strange old woman.
What is it
that you desire the most?
Enyaba: Oh,
but i’ve told you many times.
My only wish is to stay
by your side, my lord.
Your guardian spirit
has unbelievable power.
Your ability to escape trouble
and your strange life
are the result of that.
I would like to see
your life unfold.
It’s the only thing I want.
♪
Narrator: Once upon a time,
there was a prince
from the land of sumatra
who traveled the seas
seeking new lands.
Eventually he happened
upon an island
inhabited by lions
called singas,
an island he named singapura.
Today, its straits bustle
with ships and tankers
from around the world.
This nation that shares both
western and eastern heritage,
thanks to free trade,
is tropical Singapore.
Polnareff: Good grief.
We finally made it to dry land.
Joseph: We’ll clean up
and get some rest at a hotel.
Once we’ve recharged, we’ll
figure out our route to Egypt.
All right,
let’s stay at that one.
♪
( Woman chanting
in foreign language )
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian