( Waves crashing )
Man: No way! We got it.
That treasure’s been
at the bottom of the ocean
for a hundred years,
and now whatever’s in it
is ours.
Man #2: Hey, stay calm.
We gotta get it on the boat
before we start celebrating.
Man #1: Yeah, I know. I know.
Both: Up we go.
Man #3: That thing looks
too long and narrow
to be a treasure chest.
Man #1: Just do your job!
You’re lifting it too high.
Man #2: Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
Man #1: All right.
Come on. Crack it open already.
Man #3: Hold on. Wait.
This is bizarre.
It seems like this thing
was locked from the inside.
Man #1: Who the hell cares?
Just bust it open.
Man #3: Just give me a sec.
Something’s written on it.
D-i-o. "Dio."
- Is that someone’s name?
- Man #1: I don’t care!
Just freakin’ open it up!
The sun’s about to go down,
and don’t wanna be
countin’ treasure in the dark.
Man #1: Okay, I hear you.
( Grunts )
I’m gonna go get the blowtorch.
Man #1: And then we can start
dividin’ up our loot.
♪
Narrator: On a day
like any other,
a motorboat was found
adrift and abandoned.
The craft was largely undamaged
and showed no signs of struggle.
In the galley, three cups
of coffee sat half full,
and on deck, an iron chest,
its lock melted away,
lay open and empty.
But the chest’s unusual
shelter-like chambers
baffled discoverers,
who believed it to have once
contained a vast treasure.
But interest waned,
and before long,
the chest was forgotten.
Man: Jotaro kujo, 17 years old
and 195 centimeters tall.
His father is
a Japanese jazz musician,
currently on tour.
His mother is an American
of British decent.
Mrs. Kujo: Yes,
all of that is correct,
and jotaro is definitely my son.
Officer #2: It seems like
all his friends call him jojo.
Guess they decided to take
the Jo from his first name
and the Jo from his last name
and combine ’em.
Ah, man, that’s really lame.
Mrs. Kujo: I--i need to know.
Exactly how many people
did jotaro kill?!
No! I take it back!
I don’t want to know!
Officer #1: Settle down.
Nobody said anything
about him killin’ people.
Officer #2: He got into a fight.
That’s all.
Officer #1: The truth is,
the thugs he tangled with
were all armed
with nunchuks and knives.
He fought four punks,
one being an ex-boxer,
and he broke 15 of their bones,
and he busted their balls.
Sorry if that was crude.
He put all of them
in the hospital.
Officer #2: Things could
have gone a lot worse.
He’s gotta be shown
the severity of his actions.
Mrs. Kujo: Okay.
Officer #1: The real issue
is what happened afterward.
Copy this, and pass it around.
- Officer #3: Yes, sir.
- Officer #1: I gotta tell you,
that son of yours
is a strange one.
Mrs. Kujo: Huh?
Officer #1: Okay, follow me.
I’ll show you the way.
Mrs. Kujo: Thank you
for everything.
Officer #1: Look,
you can thank me
by takin’ your kid home.
Mrs. Kujo: So then, does that
mean you’re releasing him?
Officer #1: Well, we can’t
keep him in here forever.
- Mrs. Kujo: Okay.
- Officer #1: By the way, ma’am,
I have to tell you your Japanese
is really quite good.
Just how long have you
been livin’ in Japan?
Mrs. Kujo: For 20 years now.
Officer #1: Well,
that explains it, then.
Good work, men.
This place
has been overrun lately.
We got an entire backlog
of criminals
that we aren’t even able
to find cells for.
Officer #2:
We’re almost there, ma’am.
Your son’s just up ahead.
( Mrs. Kujo gasps ) Jotaro!
Young Mrs. Kujo:
Jotaro, throw the ball to mom.
( Both laugh )
Mrs. Kujo: That’s it. Good boy.
Do your best
at that track meet tomorrow.
Jotaro: I will.
Mrs. Kujo: Jotaro.
You did it. Let’s go out
to eat and celebrate.
Jotaro: Nothing’s as good
as your cooking, mom.
Mrs. Kujo: Jotaro.
Jotaro.
Jotaro!
Jotaro: Shut up!
Get out of my face, you bitch!
Mrs. Kujo: Okay!
I promise you
he’s a very sweet boy.
He’s just not capable of doing
something so appalling.
Officer #2:
Hey, on your feet, kujo!
You’re being released.
What part of "go home"
don’t you understand?
♪
- Jotaro: Hmph.
- ( Officers gasp )
Jotaro: Listen, mom,
you can leave.
I’ll be stayin’ here
for a while.
Mrs. Kujo: Huh?
Jotaro: Seems i’ve been
possessed by an evil spirit,
and i’ve no idea
what he’ll make me do next.
During that fight, it took
all I had just to stop it,
so do everyone a favor,
and leave me in this cage.
Officer #1: Jeez.
For crying out loud.
Do you see
what i’m talking about?
We’re trying to release him,
but he refuses to go.
I’m sorry to have
to ask you this,
but are you sure
everything’s all right
with your boy upstairs?
Officer #2: This isn’t a hotel,
you know, ma’am.
Prisoner: Come on!
Let us change cells! Please!
Prisoner #2: He’s not lying
about the evil spirit thing.
( Prisoners
all talking at once )
Officer #2:
All right, all right!
That’s enough!
All of you, shut up!
( Prisoners gasp )
Officer #2: Is he--seriously?
Officer #1: What are you doin’
with a beer in a jail cell?!
How did you even
get that in there?!
( Jotaro burps )
( Prisoners wailing )
Jotaro: I told you.
I’ve got an evil spirit,
and sometimes it likes
to bring me things.
Radio announcer:
They’re still in, still in.
Officer #1: What the hell?!
He’s reading "shonen jump"
while listening to a radio!
Officer #2: Sir, I-I mean,
how is this even possible?
We have a major problem here!
Jotaro: Hold it.
This might not be enough
to make you guys
keep me locked up in here,
but i’ll show you
how evil this spirit is anyway.
( Both gasp )
Jotaro: Maybe then you’ll see
why lettin’ me outta here
is a bad idea.
♪
( Mrs. Kujo gasps )
( Officer #2 gasps ) That’s
my gun he has in his hand.
- But how’d he--
- officer #1: That’s really bad.
Jotaro: You didn’t
see it just now?
Well, if you guys didn’t see
my evil spirit, then watch this.
Mrs. Kujo: No! Jotaro!
( Men scream )
( Mrs. Kujo gasps )
♪
It’s like
there’s someone behind me.
It bound itself to me
not long ago.
Mrs. Kujo: Jotaro’s grandfather
Joseph has strange powers...
But what’s happening to my son?
( Chimes ring )
- Mrs. Kujo: Papa!
- Joseph: Hmm?
Mrs. Kujo: Over here, papa!
Over here.
Joseph: Holly! Outta my way.
Holly: Oh, I can’t believe
you’re here.
( Both laugh )
Holly: Thank you for coming.
Joseph: Hey, you’re
my one and only daughter,
and if you tell me you
need me to be somewhere,
then just give me a day,
and i’ll cross the globe.
( Holly giggles) Did mom come?
Joseph: She didn’t
like me leavin’,
but I just told Suzie
that it was
official joestar corporation
business and I had to go.
( Laughs )
Thanks, papa.
Joseph: Holly, hey.
The greeting’s over.
Let go of me already.
Holly: No. I don’t wanna.
It’s been forever
since you’ve held me.
Joseph: Look at yourself.
Come on.
You’re a 45-year-old woman.
Let go.
Holly: Oh, now you’ve done it.
I’m gonna tickle you.
Tickle, tickle, tickle.
Joseph: Hey, stop that!
- No!
- Holly: Goochie-goochie goo.
Joseph: Hmm?
( Chimes ring )
Hey, what are
you clowns staring at?
Boy: Mommy.
Woman: Don’t look.
Holly: I’ll take your bag.
Joseph: By the way, Holly,
about jotaro...
( Holly gasps )
Joseph: You sure he used
the word "evil spirit"?
( Holly whimpers )
Oh, my poor little boy.
Yes. The policemen said
they couldn’t see it,
but I saw it.
It’s like he had a third arm,
and then he reached out
and grabbed the gun.
Joseph: And when
this arm came out,
no one else there
could see it but you?
Holly: That’s right.
Joseph: And aside from jotaro
saying that he’s been possessed,
you’re okay?
Did anything happen to you?
Holly: I feel totally fine,
but what do I do about jotaro?
He says he won’t leave that cell
until he finds
the cause of all this.
What am I gonna do, papa?
There, there,
my darling daughter.
You’ve got Joseph joestar
with you now.
No need to worry.
Holly: Thank you.
( Joseph snaps fingers )
Now let’s go see my grandson.
Jotaro can explain this himself.
♪
Officer #1:
It’s gettin’ spookier.
He’s got more stuff
in his cell now,
and he’s violent.
If something is possessing him,
it’s definitely
not something nice.
If word of this
gets out to my superiors,
i’ll lose my job
in a heartbeat for sure.
Joseph: He’s no longer
your problem.
I’ll be taking
my grandson home now.
Jotaro: Your grandson?
Officer #2:
Hold it. That’s far enough.
Officer #1: You’re better off
just staying where you are.
It’s dangerous.
Convince him to leave
from where you’re standing,
or I can’t---
Joseph: I’ll take my chances.
Now step aside,
and leave him to me.
Officer #1:
We won’t be held responsible.
- Joseph: Move it!
- ( Officers gasp, yell )
Holly: Jotaro,
this is your grandfather.
Whatever’s happened,
he’ll be able to help you.
Please come out
and talk to him.
Joseph: Come out.
It’s time to go home.
Jotaro: Get lost.
I didn’t ask you to come here.
You really think
you can help me,
an old man like yourself?
Sorry you came
all the way from New York,
but nobody can help me, gramps.
Joseph: Huh? Wait.
That’s the pinkie
from my prosthetic left hand.
When was he able to take it?
Jotaro: So did you see it
or even feel it?
That’s the evil spirit.
Stay away from me, or you’ll
lose what’s left of your life.
Joseph: I’ve never
seen anything like this.
He was able to deceive me
right off the bat.
That’s unbelievable.
I’m afraid I know exactly
what jotaro’s evil spirit is,
but I don’t think explaining it
to him will do any good.
He’ll understand
his situation much better
if he sees it with his own eyes.
Actually, in order for him to
truly know the danger he faces,
he needs
to experience it physically.
( Snaps fingers )
All right, avdol.
It’s your turn now.
I’d like you to meet an Egyptian
friend I met a few years ago.
Say hello to avdol.
Jotaro: Hmm?
Joseph: Do what you need to.
Just get my grandson
to leave this damn cell.
Jotaro: Back off.
You look strong enough,
but do you really think i’d
let someone chase me outta here
just ’cause
you told them to do it?
I don’t work like that.
In fact,
all you’ve done now is made me
wanna stay here even more.
Avdol: I’m afraid
this may get a little bit rough.
But in a few minutes, he’ll
be riddled with so much pain,
that he’ll be begging you
to let him out of here.
Joseph: Just do
what you gotta do.
Holly: Papa,
you can’t be serious.
Officer #1: W-wait a sec.
We can’t let you turn this--
- Joseph: Zip it, pig!
- Officers: Yes, sir!
♪
- ( Officers and Holly gasp )
- ( Joseph grunts )
( Avdol grunts )
( Spirit shrieks )
- Jotaro: But this is...
- ( Holly gasps )
Joseph: Heh. That’s right.
Avdol also has
what you’d call an evil spirit,
an evil spirit
under the complete command
of avdol’s will,
and his name is...
- ( Spirit shrieks )
- Joseph: Magician’s red!
- ( Jotaro grunts )
- ( Holly gasps )
Jotaro: It’s hot.
I feel like i’m on fire.
My arms, they’re burning.
What are these evil spirits?
Officer #1: What’s kujo doing?
Why’s he flattened himself
against the back wall?
Officer #2:
Yeah, I don’t get it.
But do you feel how hot
it’s gettin’ in here?
Look at those numbers.
That’s insane!
What’s happening?!
( Spirit grunts )
Joseph: Aha! There it is!
It’s finally shown itself,
and the fact
that it’s so clearly visible
means it’s incredibly strong.
Jotaro: Let’s do this.
- ( Bones creak )
- ( Avdol groans )
I can’t believe he’s able to
make it manifest so distinctly.
Well done.
Jotaro: Your evil spirit
is impressive, too.
So tell me, grandpa, you know
about these evil spirits?
Joseph: Of course I do.
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
when you asked me
to help get your grandson
out of this jail cell,
I had planned
on going easy on the boy,
but in light
of his tremendous power,
i’m reconsidering that.
Just one misstep
could put us all in danger.
Tell me if you want me to stop.
If not, i’ll resort
to a use of force
that could land your grandson
in the hospital.
Joseph: Like I said,
do what you gotta do.
Avdol: Yes, sir!
( Inhales )
Red bind!
Jotaro: Huh? What the...
Officer #1: What’s up
with this heat?
Officer #2: Yeah,
what the hell’s going on?
- None of this makes any sense!
- Holly: Papa,
that’s enough!
What are you doing to jotaro?
Joseph: Holly, be a good girl,
and let papa finish
what he started, okay?
Jotaro: I can’t breathe.
Holly: The evil spirit
is withdrawing.
Joseph: The heat
is restricting his breathing,
which causes
the evil spirit to weaken.
And now for the truth.
This may seem
like an evil spirit,
but it’s far from it.
Jotaro, this thing
you believe has possessed you
is actually a powerful vision
created by your own life energy.
This vision will always appear
standing by your side,
and because of that,
we call it...
A stand!
Jotaro: A stand?
Avdol: Remember aesop’s fable.
The cold wind made the traveler
pull his coat tighter,
but the heat
forced him to admit defeat.
Ready to leave
your cage now, jojo?
( Bindings creak )
Jotaro: I said it before.
I’m stayin’.
I keep hurting other people
without even knowing
i’m doing it.
Until that stops,
i’m stayin’ here.
It’s nice to meet
someone like me,
but if you keep this up,
you’ll die.
Avdol: Huh?
Officer #2: He just
broke the damn toilet.
Officer #1: Hey,
that’s destruction of property!
Jotaro: You had your chance.
( Yells )
( Stand yells )
Jotaro: All right, bastard.
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
( Stand yells )
Jotaro: What the hell?
Why’d you suddenly
turn your back on me?
We’re not done.
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
he’s left his jail cell.
I’ve accomplished
what you asked me to do, right?
♪
( Jotaro exhales )
So now what? You got me, huh?
Avdol: Not exactly.
I did have every intention
of sending you to the hospital,
but you’re stronger
than I had expected.
Jotaro: And if I had kept going
with this steel rod,
just what would you have done?
Avdol: Do not underestimate
my stand, magician’s red.
It could have easily
melted that rod midair
into a worthless puddle.
Joseph: The power avdol has
is exactly the same as yours.
If you want to know more
about this evil spirit,
you’ll need to leave this jail.
Holly: Thank you.
Thank you, jotaro.
I’m glad you finally left
that awful jail cell.
Jotaro: Why are you
such an annoying bitch?
- Holly: Okay. I don’t know.
- Joseph: Hey,
how dare you address
your own mother that way?!
And what kind
of language is that?
And stop smiling, Holly.
You’ll only encourage it.
Holly: Okay.
Jotaro: Hey, grampa,
one question.
There’s something that I can’t
quite wrap my brain around.
You seem to know
all about this...
Evil spirit, the stand,
whatever you wanna call it,
but how do you know this?
Joseph: Hmm. How do I know?
I guess I did come
all the way from New York
to explain it to you.
But in order for you
to fully understand
the whole history of it,
I must start
from the beginning.
This is part of the legacy
of the joestar family.
Take a look at these pictures.
Jotaro: What are these about?
That coffin’s
a hundred years old,
and four years ago, it was
pulled out of the Atlantic
off the coast of Africa.
Jotaro: Okay. So?
Joseph: I did a little research.
My grandfather,
Jonathan joestar,
your great-grandfather,
died while at sea.
Turns out this exact same coffin
was on that boat with him
when he died.
When they discovered it
four years ago, it was empty.
But I know
exactly what was inside it.
Avdol and I are trying
to locate him as we speak.
Jotaro: Hold on.
Did you say, "him"?
Are you suggesting there was
a person inside that thing?
Come on. How could a human being
stay buried underwater
for a hundred years?
Joseph: Because that person
is evil incarnate,
and his name is dio!
And now that he
has been awakened
from his hundred-year slumber,
it is our fate
to fight that man!
( Jotaro sighs )
Joseph: What the hell
does that face mean?
And don’t you
turn your back on me
like this has
nothing to do with you!
Jotaro: Look, you old man,
this face means
your story is so lame,
I don’t know what to say.
- Joseph: What? "Old man"?
- ( Avdol chuckles )
Jotaro: Avdol, was it?
I don’t know you, but you
are one arrogant bastard.
- And as for you, old man...
- Joseph: Huh?
Jotaro: Did you
really expect me to fall
for an unbelievable story
like that?
Avdol: Heh. I know
the story sounds far-fetched,
but wouldn’t you also say
our evil spirits
are equally unbelievable?
( Joseph scoffs )
Think what you want,
but soon you will have no choice
but to believe it.
If you want me to tell you
how I know that dio exists
and why i’ve chosen
to go after him,
the best way to explain it
is to show you.
See, the truth of it
is I myself had
a rather startling revelation
that prompted all of this.
About a year ago, I suddenly
obtained a stand of my own.
Holly: What did you say?!
Jotaro: Gramps, what did you...
Joseph: Get ready.
Let me introduce...
My stand!
♪
Did you see it, the thorns
that came out of my hand?
This is my stand.
It can reveal faraway visions
and place them on film.
The only downside
is I have to bust
a 30,000-yen camera
every time I use it!
Waiter: Excuse me.
Is everything all right here?
Avdol: We’re fine.
Now go on. Run along.
Waiter: Of course.
Joseph: In a matter of seconds,
a vision will appear
in this photograph, jotaro,
and it will reveal
your very destiny!
Jotaro: What are you
talking about?
Joseph: Jotaro, Holly,
have either of you
ever taken the time
to look carefully
at the back of your necks?
( Holly gasps )
Jotaro: What does that mean?
Joseph: You each have it,
but you probably
never thought much about it,
a birthmark shaped like a star.
It turns out
that we all have it.
( Holly gasps )
( Jotaro gasps )
I’ll say it again.
What the hell
does all this mean?
Joseph: My father died
when I was young,
so I asked my mother about it,
and she said he had one, too.
It seems that everyone
from the joestar bloodline
is born with
this exact same birthmark.
Jotaro: All right,
and just what the hell
is gonna turn up
in that photograph?
Joseph: It’s our destiny,
a path that until now
has been unknown.
Holly: Papa.
Jotaro: I’m losing my Patience.
Just show me
the damn photo already.
♪
Joseph: Dio. He shows up
in all my spirit photos,
and look what’s
just above his shoulder.
From the neck
of this bastard on down
is Jonathan joestar,
my grandfather!
This son of a bitch
took over his body!
( Both gasp )
Joseph: A hundred years ago,
there was an incident
in the Atlantic ocean.
All I know is what i’ve learned
from my grandmother, erina.
Somehow, dio took over the body
of my grandfather and survived.
And this much
I know is certain--
this bastard is currently
hiding somewhere on the globe,
plotting something.
It’s four years
since he’s revived,
and the reason
my spirit photography
and your evil spirit
have manifested since
is most likely connected to dio.
Avdol: To society in general,
our gifts are considered
a kind of psychic power.
I’ve had my stand
since the day I was born,
but your powers
seem bound to dio’s body,
or, rather,
Jonathan joestar’s body.
There’s some sort
of invisible string
that connects you all to him.
His rebirth is also your own,
awakening your sleeping powers.
Joseph: Avdol,
does this photograph
give you any indication
to where he might be now?
Avdol: No, nothing.
There’s hardly anything of note
in the photo at all.
Joseph: I see.
Avdol: I’ll take
a closer look later.
Joseph: Thank you. Hmm?
Oh, Holly.
I’m sorry I sprang this all
on you out of the blue.
- Let’s head home now.
- Holly: All right.
Joseph: I think i’ll be sticking
around for quite some time.
You mind if I stay
at your place while i’m here?
Holly: No, of course not, papa.
Let’s go, jotaro.
( Footsteps echoing )
♪
( Dio sighs )
Again...
Just now...
A most intense feeling
like someone somewhere
is watching me.
It is jonathan’s descendants.
This body is sending out
some kind of spiritual signal
to his offspring.
Fine. It must be my fate.
But fate must be purged.
It’s all set.
I’ve taken the first step.