[PEDESTRIANS chatter]
Check it out, Smile,
have you noticed?
Blood tastes kinda like iron,
that's pretty cool, right?
[STADIUM GUY 11A]
No, I want the red T-shirt.
You got it in medium?
Not that one.
The other one!
Right there in the corner.
Tanaka! Hold up,
you forgot your shoes!
Those are
Nakata's!
So three Pocaris, three oolong,
two Posts, two Vaams,
and two Gatorades.
Plus an Aquarius and--
[STADIUM GUY 11E]
Write it down!
[STADIUM GUY 11A]
The red one!
How many times do
I have to tell you?
I mean they're both on our team,
who are we supposed to root for?
You got me.
Injury?
No, no, I was a hundred percent.
My conditioning has
never been better
and I gave that match
everything I had.
I lost simply because I wasn't
good enough to beat him.
[STADIUM GUY 11F]
Man it's hot.
Dude Sakuma, seriously,
what's with the hair?
Trying a little too
hard to be cool, bro.
[KAIO PLAYERS laugh]
[SAKUMA]
Yeah, maybe.
Hey, anyone'd want to show off
after becomin' a free man.
Y'should stop by
sometime, though.
Coach still worries about you.
[MALE COMMITTEE MEMBER 11A]
Mr. Koizumi's boys sure are
a surprise, aren't they?
Old Butterfly Jo's
definitely left his mark.
Tsukimoto's style really
reminds me of him.
Could you do me a favor
and pitch my college to 'im
if you get a chance?
I want the hitter,
he's got potential.
Could be one'a
the greats.
[STADIUM GUY 11G]
When does it start?
[STADIUM GUY 11H]
Ten more minutes.
Ha, ha, ha, ha! Dude!
Seriously?
[MALE STAFF 11A yawns]
[KONG, in Chinese]
Do you want coffee or tea?
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Either one.
Make a decision.
Coffee, then.
[PLAYER GUY 11C, in English]
You're not gonna watch
the finals?
[PLAYER GUY 11D] Makes no
difference to us, does it?
[EGAMI] The finals are
between two Katase players?
Not Kaio Academy?
Tsukimo--
[EGAMI gasps]
It can't be.
[STADIUM GUY 11A]
Okay, just follow the finger.
No, my finger, you dolt!
[MIC CHECK GUY 11A]
Uh, testing. Testing.
Mic check.
Mic check, one two three.
No, Kaio's not in it!
They're both from Katase
High School man, yeah!
Kazama lost in the semis.
I'm dead serious!
[SPECTATORS chatter]
Huh?
How's everything
going, Captain Ota?
Don't see Hoshino.
He isn't
here yet.
[KOIZUMI] Yeah, his knee
can't be gettin' any better
at this point, huh?
[OTA] Well he's not exactly
givin' me updates.
[TAKAMURA] All right Coach.
Help us out here.
Which one do we root for?
[KOIZUMI]
Both, Mr. Takamura.
We're going to cheer when either
one of them scores a point.
Are you ready, Mr. Tsukimoto?
Do ya think you
could've done that?
Rubbed salt in an
old friend's wound?
Used a strategy that might've
ended his career for good.
Could you really
have done that?
I know how to
play 'im, Coach.
It's simple.
If the opponent has
a weak right knee,
serve deep to forehand then
switch to his backhand.
[TAKAMURA] What?!
You're seriously goin' all
"sweep the leg" on him?
I thought he was
your best friend!
Here's a question for
you, Mr. Tsukimoto.
What happens when you target
a true hero's weak points?
[TSUKIMOTO] True heroes
don't have weak points.
[KOIZUMI] Hm.
All right, son; fair enough.
Let's just see how
this unfolds, shall we?
You really are the
best player I know.
Now on Court Six.
The final match!
Hoshino of Katase High School
against Tsukimoto of Katase!
What's the deal,
Captain Ota?
Where's your
other player?
[OTA]
Uh...!
[SCHOOL BOY 11A] Hey, did you
see Hoshino's math test?
[SCHOOL BOY 11C]
Yeah, he got a zero!
[SCHOOL BOY 11B] I can't
believe how dumb he is!
He said he'd be out today.
With the usual excuse.
Well that's
some good news.
Won't be
so noisy.
Hey, Golgo!
Go buy me some coffee-milk
from the machine.
And make it quick.
If you want something to drink,
then go buy it yourself.
Whoa, now!
You short circuit?
Think you can talk back like
that 'cause Hoshino's gone?
Robots aren't allowed
to disobey humans.
Don't you know the
Three Laws of Robotics?
So move it, droid!
Or we'll stick you
in your locker again.
[SCHOOL BOY 11B]
Shut up, we're in trouble!
Hoshino's here!
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
That's right I am!
Thank you for the introduction!
Oh god!
Wait! I didn't--
[SCHOOL BOY 11B]
Aahh!
[SCHOOL BOY 11A]
Stop! Get off me!
Just laugh when something's
funny, and yell when you're mad.
You make it so hard on yourself.
I hate watching it.
'Kay, I'm sorry.
I'll try harder.
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] Tsh.
You're such a weirdo.
I don't get you at all.
Anyway Hoshino, how come
you're always skipping class?
Do you hate school?
You don't know?
I go play ping pong.
Ping pong, huh?
Yeah look in my bag
and see for yourself.
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)] Oh.
[HOSHINO (CHILD)] Today was
Yokohama, next week's Chiba.
I go to all the meets I can.
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
So you're good at it?
Unbeatable!
Whoa!
[SAKUMA (CHILD) grunts]
Ha! Give it three hundred
years more practice, Akuma,
y'might stand a chance!
[SAKUMA (CHILD)]
Yeah, yeah, shut up.
Tsukimoto, c'mere!
Huh?
You should try
playing a game with us.
No thanks,
I'm fine.
It's enough fun just
watching you guys.
[SAKUMA (CHILD)] Oh please.
Isn't he that nerd
from Class Three?
What's he doing here?
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
You can't "get" this game
just by watching it.
It's not like a
stupid math test.
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
I don't know.
Don't worry, pal,
I'll teach you!
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)] Hm.
Viva!
Cuttin' it awfully close.
Heh. Aw, gimme a break.
I got here just
as fast as I could.
[TSUKIMOTO] Yeah.
[HOSHINO]
Let's do this, partner.
[TSUKIMOTO] Yeah.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Deep to the forehand,
then switch to his
backhand side.
[HOSHINO laughs]
[SPECTATORS cheer]
[TSUKIMOTO]
Blood tastes like iron.
Careful, you're not allowed
to close your fingers
around the ball.
And you have to
hold your hand up
so it's higher than the table.
Also, your serve's gotta
bounce once on your side.
You get it, Tsukimoto?
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
Mm-hm.
Cool, give it a shot.
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
Okay. I'll try.
[SPECTATORS cheer]
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
It's safe and quiet in here.
I'm comfortable.
I won't make a sound.
Like a robot.
[footsteps]
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
Someone's coming!
No, it's okay.
I can stay in here.
If I don't make a sound,
I'll be fine.
I won't get mad.
I won't laugh, or anything.
I'll just be!
I won't even breathe!
If I go outside...
it'll happen again!
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
You're wrong, Smile.
Check it out, Smile,
have you noticed?
Blood tastes kinda like iron,
that's pretty cool, right?
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)]
What's that s'posed to mean?
I don't get it.
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
Let's play ping pong, Smile.
♪ Ping pong, ping pong,
we all love ping pong! ♪
Come on, I'll teach you how!
[HOSHINO yells]
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
Yeah, that's great! You're good!
Put your back into it!
Ooh, look at that!
Awesome!
This is what we look
like on the inside?
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
Now check this out!
I can see through to my blood.
That's why it's red!
You try, Smile. Go on!
There, you see?
I toldja you've got blood
flowing in you too!
It's just as red as mine!
Go hard, Smile,
you have to!
A man's gotta have
true grit to survive!
Destroy!
[TSUKIMOTO yells]
[TSUKIMOTO groans]
Smile!
Comin' back at'cha, Smile!
[TSUKIMOTO grunts]
[TSUKIMOTO yells]
Yeah!
[SPECTATORS cheer and applaud]
[HOSHINO]
Ha, ha, ha!
Give it another three hundred
years practice, Smile!
[TSUKIMOTO] My blood
tastes like iron.
My blood tastes like iron.
[in Chinese] Looks like
his knee is all right.
[in Chinese] Yeah.
[in English]
It was careless of us
not to keep an eye on that dude.
Heh. Wouldn't have changed
a thing, even if we had.
S'a rare moment for that boy.
Peco's the only one he can have
fun playin' all-out against.
Yeah but Mom,
what about his knee?
Oh, I'm sure
it's killing him.
So back in the day...
did you try to stop
Dragon's grampa?
[MICHIO laughs]
Sorry, just wondering 'bout
the good old days, Mom.
You don't have to say.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
[TSUKIMOTO]
The hero transcends logic.
The hero takes the world
we thought we knew,
and turns it on its head.
He drives away the darkness.
He's uncomplicated.
A straight-shooter.
And he shines,
bright and joyous.
Yeah!
[SPECTATORS cheer]
[EGAMI] I'll be damned.
I do like this sport.
I left you, and
wandered the world,
searching for
where I belonged.
But all this time,
the answer was you.
I'm so sorry table tennis,
my perfect queen.
Will you forgive me?
Can't we just start over?
I swear I'll never
leave you again!
[TAMURA sighs]
[KOIZUMI]
You all right, Tamura?
Thought you were just
on a bathroom break.
[TAMURA] Hm.
Standing too long takes
a toll on these old bones.
It's not like it matters
who wins this one, anyway.
Make sure you take Hoshino to
the hospital when this is over.
It's only adrenaline
that's keeping him upright.
Trust me.
I'm well aware.
[KOIZUMI] Mm.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Hey there.
Long time no see.
Look Tamura, it's
the CEO of Poseidon.
You're a hell of a
cutthroat businessman, Ryu.
Can't believe you're peddling
your mats to high schoolers now.
Here I thought building a
winning team and trusted brand
would make everyone happy.
But Ryuichi and
Yurie are moving on.
And my son is too.
You've put on some weight.
So tell me old man, who do
you play table tennis for?
For all of us,
of course.
What a load of horse shit.
I wouldn't expect anything
else from you, though.
[KOIZUMI] I hear you've been
telling people you beat me
through sheer grit
and strength of will.
'Stead'a me bein' a
softy and lettin' ya win.
Please. Can we leave
that in the past?
I was really torn up about
that for years, you know.
How 'bout we play a match?
Huh?
Don't look at me to get
involved in this silliness,
I'm staying out.
Got a bad knee of my own.
[KAIO PRESIDENT]
Aw, come on!
You won't even have to move!
I've got a great racket
for senior citizens.
[KOIZUMI laughs]
[KOIZUMI]
Wow, hear that, Tamura?
He's trying to
sell to you, now.
[inaudible]
[TSUKIMOTO (CHILD)] Do you think
I'll ever be like you, Peco?
I wanna be just like you.
[KATASE PLAYERS yell]
[SPECTATORS cheer]
[CHILDREN sing in Japanese]
[TAMURA] Smile. Don't just
turn 'em loose all day.
I want you to teach.
[TSUKIMOTO] Mm.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Everybody, huddle up!
[CLUB CHILDREN]
Okay Coach!
I shall now teach you
a serve so unhittable,
you shall conquer the galaxy!
[CLUB CHILDREN] Yay!
[TAMURA] At least
try to be serious.
Yo.
[CLUB CHILDREN chatter]
It's Kazama,
live in the flesh!
You'll get pollen on you.
You're awesome,
Dragon!
Like the coolest!
[KAZAMA] You kiddos
been having fun?
[CLUB BOY 11C] Aw, yeah!
[CLUB BOY 11A]
You look like a gangster!
Hey, Tamura, been too long.
I brought a little
bouquet for you.
[TAMURA] Be still
my beating heart.
Not even sure I have a vase.
D'you have some time
to catch up, Tsukimoto?
He's busy.
I can go.
What?!
[TAMURA] Yeesh.
Guy hardly coaches
when he's here,
and now he's skippin'
out entirely.
Doesn't get it from me,
that's for sure.
[TAMURA] Let's go, brats!
Hop to it!
[CLUB CHILDREN]
Okay, Coach!
You need something?
The hot pot.
Where is it?
You wanna make
stew in June?
Makoto's coming today, dear.
[MRS. KOIZUMI] Yes,
but not until dinner!
It's barely past noon!
[KOIZUMI] Just help me find
the damn thing, wouldja?
[KAZAMA]
Middle school teacher?
Not sure I would'a pegged you
for that kinda career, man.
I start student
teaching next week.
It's a cryin' shame.
You could'a been a brilliant
pro athlete, Tsukimoto.
One'a the best.
Well thanks.
You're the only one
who still tells me that kinda
stuff these days, Kazama.
And I have to admit it's
nice hearing it again.
[KAZAMA] Ah!
Aw.
[TSUKIMOTO laughs]
[KAZAMA] Damn it!
[KAZAMA] So I don't
know if you keep up,
but I got cut from
the National Team.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Yeah, I heard.
Kong's doing well these days.
[KAZAMA] I used to hate
my father so much
for the life he chose.
But lately I'm feeling
more and more like him.
I worry sometimes.
That I'll become an
unremarkable player
who only dreams
about the glory days.
Who cares if you do?
Not me.
I like unremarkable, actually.
[KAZAMA] Yeah well,
I'm not okay with it!
Dumbass.
[SPECTATORS chatter]
[GERMAN ANNOUNCER, in German]
We'll now begin the fifth match!
[in English] Hey Peco!
That's you, move yer butt!
[HOSHINO]
Whoops! Coming!
[GERMAN ANNOUNCER, in German]
The Japanese ace aiming for
the top in a sport where China
dominates the world rankings!
Yutaka Hoshino!
[SPECTATORS cheer]
[HOSHINO, in English]
Yo! Danke, danke!
I love 'ya, guys!
[TSUKIMOTO] Y'hear Akuma's
wife's pregnant again?
[KAZAMA]
Their third now, right?
Yeah.
He's gonna buy his own
truck and go independent.
Says he won't be able to
come by the dojo for a while.
[KAZAMA] Really?
Ah! Damn!
[TSUKIMOTO] Needs money
to feed all those babies.
Oh, and the woman
from the Poseidon ads
was in the news, wasn't she?
[KAZAMA]
You do keep up.
[TSUKIMOTO] Everything's
on the web these days.
You actually
look us up online?
Yeah, I do.
[KAZAMA] Damn it!
What about you?
Have a girlfriend?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Wouldn't you like to know?
[KAZAMA]
That's a yes!
I wonder.
Did I go wrong somewhere?
You know what.
Maybe staking your life on
table tennis isn't so bad.
Won't be doin' that again.
No way.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Summer is coming soon.
[KAZAMA] Yup.
[TSUKIMOTO] We're getting
back into busy season.
[KAZAMA]
No doubt.
[yawns]
M'sleepy.
[KAZAMA] Heh.
[clack]