Come on, don't fall for a
simple spin shot like that!
Moron!
[HOSHINO (CHILD)]
Hey!
Stop it, Akuma!
Don't hit Smile, he's my friend!
But he's dumb, Peco!
I can't teach him,
he just keeps sucking!
Oh, Peco.
Whoops, sorry.
Should I know who you are?
[SAKUMA]
That return was horrible.
What is he doing?
[MALE UMPIRE 3A]
Match goes to Kong!
[gasping]
What the hell
were you thinking?
A game like that is bad for
everyone, the players, the fans!
Don't ever do it again!
Take a swing at
me all you want,
but don't mess
up my glasses.
That's just mean.
Not telling ya
what to do, Coach,
but isn't that kinda harsh?
He won two games against
Kong, that's not bad!
This is not a sport
for dickin' around
or not givin' a
squat about winning!
You want to try or quit?
[TSUKIMOTO]
Quit, I guess.
Then quit!
[YAMADA]
Hey, Tsukimoto!
[OTA]
Bro, hold up!
[KOIZUMI]
Let him go.
[HOSHINO]
He's such a softy.
He doesn't get it.
[HOSHINO]
Winning is everything.
[OTA]
Where ya going?
[TAMURA]
What's wrong, grampa?
The kid giving you
fifty year-old flashbacks?
[KOIZUMI]
Mrs. Tamura.
You know he's not the type
you can slap into
submission, right?
Yes, I'm aware.
[TAMURA] And I hope
you also understand
why they call him Smile.
Because he hardly ever does.
[in Chinese]
You'll go to Nationals
if you win the
next one, Wenge.
For all intents and purposes,
your match with Kazama
is the finals match.
The sloppy serves you've been
making today won't work on him.
[in Chinese]
He was in control of the game.
That's ridiculous.
Don't go there, Wenge.
[KONG, in Chinese]
I think he lost on purpose.
[in Chinese]
No, he didn't.
[buzzer]
[MALE STAFF 4A] Now on Court
Six, the quarterfinal match.
Hoshino of Katase High School
and Sakuma of Kaio Academy.
It's been a while since
we played each other, huh?
Yes.
About four years
and three months.
You've won ninety-two
games to my twenty-four.
[HOSHINO]
Hm. Double pips.
[SAKUMA] Dude, you're
the only one who plays
single-side
pips-out these days.
[HOSHINO]
Wow.
Reverse-penhold
backhand and long pips?
Interesting.
[SAKUMA]
Times are changing.
[HOSHINO]
Won't change the results.
[SAKUMA] I've dreamed
of this a long time--
Getting to play you again.
Well that's a little
melodramatic, don'tcha think?
[SAKUMA]
Sure, make it a joke.
I don't expect
you to understand.
[SAKUMA]
You were always the best.
Everything you did was so
cool and sophisticated.
We followed you like
eager little lemmings.
If you turned right,
we all turned right.
If you smiled, we all smiled.
You were a bigmouth clown, sure,
but when the game
was on the line,
you scored
every single time.
You'd even crush
the older kids
without breaking a sweat.
You don't know how
it felt watching you,
stuck in your wake.
Gotcha!
Crappy play.
Yeah!
What's wrong, Akuma?
You're playing all timid,
like you're scared.
Why don't we play a speed round?
Like we used to,
back in the day.
Yes!
[HOSHINO]
Come on!
Damn it, stop!
[chuckles]
[HOSHINO groans]
That's out!
Game goes to Sakuma!
[CROWD cheering]
What the hell!
That was cheap.
You're not attacking back.
It's all just blocks and lobs.
Table tennis
is an evolving game.
Your approach is so outdated
it belongs in a
natural history museum.
School is in
session, candy addict!
And I'll end this quick so
I don't miss Kazama's match!
[SAKUMA] I know how
you made fun of me.
You called me
"Professor Ping Pong"
for trying to
learn from books.
But you know what?
Sometimes preparation pays off.
[SAKUMA]
You were the golden boy.
Like your rubbers and
blades actually shined.
[frustrated growl]
[SAKUMA] I had to
sit there and clap,
while you showed off all
those medals and trophies.
You can't understand
what it was like,
watching you flaunt your talent.
But talent isn't everything.
It only takes you so far.
Eventually hard work and
determination are required.
You're nowhere near the
player Kazama is now.
[SAKUMA]
Yes!
Yah!
Your game's still dripping
with laziness and resignation.
You don't stand a chance.
We've left you in our dust!
[MALE UMPIRE 3A]
Match point.
Sakuma!
[chuckles]
Akuma. You bastard!
[MALE UMPIRE 3A]
Match to Sakuma!
[CROWD cheering]
[SAKUMA]
Peco.
You must hate losing,
considering you've never
had to deal with it before,
so let me tell you a secret to
spare you all that future pain.
The only way to not
lose is to not fight.
[SAKUMA laughs]
Quit the sport now if you're
just gonna keep coasting along!
No one wants to see you
cry all over the tables.
[yells]
[TAMURA] Crazy how I used to
play like life depended on it.
I'd wear the same
lucky headband for weeks.
You were beautiful when we
were in high school, Tamura.
Amazingly strong too.
A real joy to watch.
Victory meant
everything in those days.
If someone lost, we'd
attack their whole character.
"Losers are history.
And winners get to write it."
But that kind of thinking
is just plain destructive.
I've seen it ruin lives.
I'm not sure it's
all that different today.
[TAMURA] Your boy sure
breaks the mold, doesn't he?
Incredibly talented,
but he doesn't give
a lick about winning.
I think it's just the
way the world works.
Some of the most gifted people
are so comfortable with who
they are they don't care about
achievements. They've
got nothing to prove.
I'm not trying to
force this on him.
He can make his own choice.
But how can he make
a real decision
until he understands
what the options are?
I just want to give him a chance
to see the view at the
top of the mountain first.
And I think once he does,
something inside him
is gonna change.
[TAMURA]
You sure about that?
Bullying Tsukimoto won't bring
back your youth, you know.
You can't rewrite the past.
Good work.
[SAKUMA]
Thank you, sir.
Wait a sec, where's Kazama?
[TAKU]
He's off in the can.
Again.
[SAKUMA] Why, is he
constipated or something?
[TAKU]
No.
Nothin' like that.
He does this before every match.
Holes up somewhere private.
[toilet flushes]
It's about time
we got to a boss fight.
I hear he's won
sixty-eight in a row.
The guy really
is a monster, isn't he?
I heard at Kaio
if you lose before
the fourth round,
they kick you off the team.
[MALE PLAYER 4B]
No way, seriously?
That's freaking harsh.
[MALE PLAYER 4A] Table tennis
is their whole life.
They're obsessed.
[MALE PLAYER 4B]
It's kind of scary, actually.
[MALE PLAYER 4A]
Check out Kazama.
He's got a look in his
eyes like he killed a man.
And who knows, maybe he has.
If that news came out,
I wouldn't be shocked.
Shh!
He's gonna hear you,
you dumbass!
Just look at him,
tell me how he's
still in high school.
Dude's gotta be
thirty years old, minimum.
Now on Court Eight,
the quarterfinal match
between Kong Wenge
of Tsujido High School
and Ryuichi Kazama,
Kaio Academy.
[CROWD GUY 4A]
Go Kazama!
[CROWD GUY 4B]
Win it all!
[CROWD GUY 4C]
Wipe the floor with this guy!
[CROWD GUY 4D]
Have my babies!
[in Chinese]
Ah, so he's the hero
of this little
island country.
[in Chinese]
Look at those muscles.
He's got power, but I doubt
he's light on his feet.
Make a good serve,
then do a
third ball attack.
Keep in the lead
from start to finish.
[KONG, in Chinese]
Easy for you to say.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Have confidence.
You're the stronger player.
[CROWD cheering]
[KONG, in Chinese]
Heh, lively crowd.
[MALE UMPIRE 3A]
First game.
Service to Kong.
Love all.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Yes!
So fast!
[KONG, in Chinese]
He's good.
[SAKUMA chuckling]
[in Chinese]
I can't believe how fast
his reaction time is.
A real monster, huh?
[KONG, in Chinese] He must
have a hole in his defenses
somewhere!
[KONG, in Chinese]
Somewhere!
He's reading me.
He's predicting my moves!
[KONG, in Chinese]
Show me your weak point!
I can't afford to end here!
Not here!
[KONG, in Chinese]
My...
My drive will!
[CROWD cheering]
[KONG panting]
[MALE UMPIRE 3A]
Match to Kazama!
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
Your girlfriend?
[KONG, in Chinese]
No, my mother.
She made me carry it.
[in Chinese] She's the
stereotypical country parent.
[in Chinese] How long have
you lived away from her?
[in Chinese]
Since I was eight.
That's when I joined
the provincial team.
[KONG, in Chinese] After that,
she brought me food once a week.
She worked in a candy factory,
and she'd bring
mountains of their candy.
[CHINESE COACH, in Chinese]
You didn't like
anything she brought?
[KONG, in Chinese]
Hm...
Her homemade wontons were great.
I used to dream
I'd lost my keys.
It'd be a relief not
to have anymore dreams
where I'm the only
one without a ticket.
[in Chinese]
Wenge.
Your life has just begun.
You've only just
reached the starting line.
[in Chinese]
I'm done for.
I don't mean table tennis.
I'm talking about life.
And this isn't
your coach talking.
This is the opinion of a
friend who knows you well.
[KONG laughs]
[KONG, in Chinese]
It helps.
[KAZAMA]
S'cuse me, Tsukimoto?
Can we talk for a minute?
Are you heading
back to your school?
[KAZAMA]
Yes.
We're still having practice.
[TSUKIMOTO]
That's hardcore.
[KAZAMA] As players, my
teammates are mostly useless.
They don't even realize
it, which makes it worse.
You know how it is.
[TSUKIMOTO]
Huh?
Come to Kaio, Smile.
I can make it real
comfortable for you there.
[KAZAMA]
As I'm sure you know,
Kaio Academy was founded by
a former table tennis star,
so you won't find a school more
passionate about the sport.
We have dedicated
practice facilities open
around the clock,
with international coaches
training us every
morning and evening.
All of our practices are filmed
in HD and analyzed by computer.
We have state-of-the-art
machines that can replicate
almost any shot, and
others to collect the balls.
Equipment is provided free.
It's all professional grade, and
you can use as much as you like.
You'll never worry
about rubber care again.
We restock every
three or four days.
You have your choice
of the best new rubbers
from a mountain of options,
so they're pristine
for every match.
Our specialists will also
help custom-tailor equipment
to your own style of play.
You'll have a
personalized weight training
and cardio program, too.
The trainers in our gym employ
the latest sports science
to understand and keep
your body in top shape.
All meals are
supervised by nutritionists.
And I'm still only
scratching the surface.
Have you ever
wanted to play overseas?
The staff is looking out
for our long-term futures.
There's a full library
where you can find coverage
of every major
international competition.
And if you ask, someone'll
go record any match you want,
anywhere in the world.
You can't reach Nationals alone,
much less the world stage.
But you have talent, Tsukimoto.
Katase isn't worthy of you.
You belong with us at Kaio.
I'll come pick ya up one day.
When you're ready.
Yeah, good luck
at the championships.
Where the hell is Kazama?
Guy definitely takes his
sweet time in the can.
All your play was sloppy!
That's unacceptable!
You clowns think you're so
good you can pull your punches
against inferior players?
Well at Nationals, you
boys're gonna be screwed!
--Sir!
[TAKU]
When we get back to the gym,
I want everyone to
show me you're serious.
Understood?
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes sir!
[TAKU]
Dismissed!
Yurie!
You're only now getting here?
Ah well, Ryuichi,
you ride back with her.
[KAZAMA]
Yes, sir.
[KAIO PLAYER 4A]
Is that Coach's daughter?
[KAIO PLAYER 4B]
She's hot.
[KAIO PLAYER 4C] Yeah, have you
seen her in those commercials?
[KAIO PLAYER 4B]
Kazama's one lucky dog.
[KAIO PLAYER 4D] Yeah,
I hear he lives with her
at the President's house.
He actually has a life.
[SANADA]
It isn't right.
[TAKU]
Those two are cousins!
Their relationship is platonic.
[KAIO PLAYER 4B]
No way I'm buying that.
[KAIO PLAYER 4A]
Dads are totally blind.
[TAKU]
You'll pay for that in laps!
Get on the bus!
[KAIO PLAYERS]
Yes sir!
[announcement bell]
[MALE STAFF 4A] Attention,
ladies and gentlemen.
All of today's
matches have ended,
concluding this year's
qualifying round.
Thank you again for attending,
and we look forward
to seeing you next time.
The building will
close promptly at six.
We ask that you exit
in a timely manner.
We apologize
for any inconvenience.