[NAGISA] Koro-sensei:
A mysterious super being
who's blown up half the moon
and vows to destroy Earth
by March of next year.
The powers that be have a bounty
on his head: Ten-billion yen.
We're Class 3-E of
Kunugigaoka Junior High,
also known as the End Class.
And believe it or not,
we're the misfits who're
supposed to assassinate him.
Even though we'd pinpointed
some of his weaknesses
before summer vacation,
we still haven't managed
to hit our target.
This is Class 3-E:
The Assassination Classroom.
The bell rings,
another day begins.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[NAGISA] Our "assassination
vacation" was almost over.
Almost, but not quite.
We'd decided to make the most of
what little time we
had left on Okinawa.
A test of courage?
On our last day here?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of course!
What better activity for
a fine midsummer's night?
Yeah, nice try. You just wanna
have fun at our expense.
[KORO-SENSEI] Unlike some
who shall remain nameless,
I've been too cooped up in a
shell to have any fun at all!
We're on a tropical island,
for cryin' out loud!
I think a test of courage
sounds like a blast!
No kidding!
Aww. But I don't
like being scared.
Don't worry! Koro-Sensei'll
be playing the ghosts, right?
Oh yeah.
[SUGINO]
So it won't be scary.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[NAGISA] There's no way we
could've known at the time,
but Koro-sensei's real purpose
wasn't just to scare us.
[KORO-SENSEI] This ocean
cavern is the ideal spot.
I want everyone to walk
through in boy-girl pairs.
So, uh, you're not bothered
by this kind of thing?
Nah. I don't mind spooky
stuff so much, actually.
Jump scares, though,
I'm not a real big fan of.
Don't be surprised
if I freak out a bit.
With Koro-sensei
as quick as he is,
he's bound to catch
me once or twice.
Hm? Is that an Okinawa
shamisen playing?
[BOTH]
Oh no!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Beware.
You have entered a cave
drenched in blood and tragedy.
For here, routed in battle,
members of the Ryukyu royalty
met a most terrible
and violent end.
Is that actually true?
Possibly,
but odds are he's just making
it up to create atmosphere.
[KORO-SENSEI] You would be
wise to stay together.
Anyone left alone in this cave
will be haunted
by restless spirits!
[BOTH gasp]
You gotta admit it's starting
to sound kind of authentic.
I vote we go through
as quickly as we can.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Beware.
You have entered a cave
drenched in blood...
Hearing him give his
spiel to the next couple
adds to the realism.
Now that's what I call spooky.
[NAKAMURA, ISOGAI scream]
[chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] No question my
students have gotten stronger.
But as far as they've come,
there's still a little
something missing.
Specifically....
...a love scandal!
A few were on the
verge of pairing off
before the summer break,
but they've been so
hyper-focused on assassination
no one's had time
to spark a romance!
Thankfully, there's nothing
quite like abject terror
for bringing two
people together.
I'll get material yet.
For my trashy,
based-on-a-true-story,
mass-market novel about
love-struck teenagers!
Let no one say I don't
have a big heart!
[chuckling]
[OKUDA] Afraid of not being
afraid? I don't get it.
Look.
When Nagisa faced off with
Takoka, it knocked me on my ass.
And not 'cause he beat him.
[KARMA] The way he was
during the whole thing,
it was like, I dunno...
He wasn't the
least bit affected.
I mean, in a fight,
I'd win. We all know that.
But to an assassin, winning
a fight doesn't mean squat.
That's when it dawned on me.
What scared me most of
all was not being afraid.
Still, though.
I won't lose.
I'll definitely be the one
who ends our teacher's life.
Take my word for it.
Okay! I can't wait to see who
finally winds up killing him.
Hang on a second.
[OKUDA]
Huh?
[KARMA] Wasn't this supposed
to be a test of courage?
'Cause it's lookin'
to me like the Octopus
has something a little
different in mind.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Urgh.
Why are none of these kids
falling for each other?
Next couple for sure!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Beware.
You have entered a cave
drenched in blood and tragedy.
For here-- Ah! Monster!
[KORO-SENSEI screaming]
I've been scaring
the crap out of people
since I was little girl.
They don't call me Miss
Courage Tester for nothin'.
Scariest girl in Japan.
Okay.
Well as long as you're enjoying
yourself I guess, right?
[panting]
[KORO-SENSEI] That was only an
average g-g-ghost, wasn't it?
Not the restless spirit
of Ryukyu royalty? Ah!
Oh! He has no eyes!
Ah! I felt something slithery!
Oh! Creepy Japanese Doll!
Ah! Horror manga-ka
Shigeru Mizuki!
Oh! I'm not even sure what
this is, but I feel like...
[KAEDE] Kinda weird he's more
freaked out than any of us.
[NAGISA]
Yeah. We, uh, we should go.
[KORO-SENSEI panting]
[KORO-SENSEI] Good gracious.
What an unmitigated disgrace.
So let me get this straight.
This whole thing was about
scaring us into hookin' up
so you could have
material for a book?
[TOKA] We so knew that's
what you were doing.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What's wrong with wanting to see
tender feelings blossom between
two bright, young things
before their best
years are behind them
and they wind up stuck
in loveless mar...
[HINANO]
Well, this is awkward.
[SUGAYA]
Are we sure he's an adult?
Not that we don't appreciate
the thought and all,
but, come on, we're just kids.
Did it ever occur to you
that maybe some of us
don't feel like being
in a relationship?
And no offense, but isn't
shipping us sorta creepy.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I know. I'm sorry.
[IRINA] Pathetic. You call
that a test of courage?
There was no one in
there! What a waste.
You can let go of
my arm any day now.
This is not what I need
after an all-nighter.
Ugh! Shut up!
You're a man, aren't ya?
It's your damn responsibility
to escort pretty women!
[KARASUMA sighs]
[IRINA laughing nervously]
[MAEHARA] Hey. So is anyone
thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
[HINANO]
That Professor Bitch is...?
[TOKA]
Uh-huh.
[MAEHARA]
Should we do something?
[NAKAMURA] We don't head
home till tomorrow morning,
so there's time.
[KORO SENSEI]
Then let's hook them up.
[NAGISA] Our final operation on
the island was about to start.
Turns out we're just as into
shipping as Koro-sensei.
[IRINA] Ugh! You're killin' me!
The man's so obtuse!
Isn't that a bit out
of character for you?
You're supposed to be
known for wrapping guys
around your little finger.
But when it comes
to her own love life,
she doesn't have a clue.
Oh, knock it off. Love?
Don't make me laugh!
[MAEHARA]
What? You're not in love?
No! I'm attracted
to the challenge
of conquering a
world-class square!
I just wanted to see if I
could make him fall for me,
that's all.
And I got... carried away.
[ALL gasp]
[SUGINO]
That was kind of adorable.
[MAEHARA]
More like embarrassing.
Don't judge me!
[NAGISA] Professor Bitch
is a lot more awkward
than she first comes off.
Maybe all the stuff
she's had to do
makes it hard for her
to own her feelings.
[MAEHARA] Hey. It's cool,
really. We've got this!
[IRINA]
Huh?
Let us set the stage and
you can take it from there.
Yeah!
Well, if you think you can.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent!
In that case,
I call the Class 3-E Love
Consultant Meeting to order.
[IRINA]
Eager much, Octopus?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Come now, it's only natural
to encourage romance
between colleagues.
A female educator aching for the
touch of her stoic counterpart.
If that's not a trashy
best-seller in the making,
I don't know what is!
Uh, I think you're planning
something racier than we are.
[MAEHARA]
If we're gonna do this right,
we need to start by overhauling
your fashion sense.
[IRINA]
Hm?
[NAKAMURA] I'll say. Revealing
might be appealing for some,
but parading the
goods doesn't cut it
for stuffed shirt
like Mr. Karasuma.
Your wardrobe should be
more... understated.
Understated? Huh, okay then.
Use the way Kanzaki dresses as
a model and you can't go wrong.
As a matter of fact. Is what
you wore yesterday dry?
Yeah. Of course.
[NAKAMURA] See? It makes
you look like a, uh--
[ALL] How in the world did
that make her even sexier?
[SUGAYA]
Well, to begin with,
the fit's a little
snug in places.
Man, I don't even
wanna tell you
what I think about when
Kankazi's in that thing.
Fine.Whatever. Huge
boobs we can work with.
Not like we have a choice,
and bust size doesn't really
matter that much anyway.
[KORO-SENSEI] Have we
established Mr. Karasuma's type?
Yeah! That girl in the ad.
I think he's, I don't know,
utterly infatuated with her?
Said she's his ideal
type, or something.
[KARASUMA] Whoo boy.
Now that's the whole package.
And the best part?
There are three of 'em!
[ALL] He meant his
ideal military type!
Well, the quickest way to a
man's heart is his stomach.
They serve some pretty
good stuff here.
We could arrange it
so the two of you
eat his favorite dish
together on the beach.
[MAEHARA] Trouble is,
I've only ever seen the guy
eat burgers and cup ramen, so...
[NAKAMURA] Doesn't exactly set
the mood for a romantic evening.
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
[KORO-SENSEI] This match
was doomed from the start!
[MAEHARA]
Yeah,
I'm starting the think maybe
the problem is Mr. Karasuma.
See? He's such an idiot!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I should've seen it before.
A man who never laughs at
my jokes is a lost cause!
[NAGISA]
With no other options,
we settled for insulting
Mr. Karasuma.
[KORO-SENSEI]
There's no help for it.
Even so, let's do what
we can before dinner.
The ladies are in charge
of hair and makeup.
The gentlemen are
tasked with setting
just the right ambiance
for the table.
[STUDENTS]
Roger!
We're supposed to be
eating as a group, right?
So, where do I sit?
Well not here obviously.
It looks like there
isn't enough room.
Is our favorite teacher trying
to force his way into a seat?
Honestly, you'd just
get in the way here.
How about you be a
good sport about it
and eat your dinner
outside, okay?
[KARASUMA]
Huh?
Where did that come
from all of a sudden?
I mean I realize I'm out of
touch with young people,
but seriously.
Hm?
Why the hell'd just the
two of us get kicked out?
[IRINA]
Oh, uh. Who knows?
So, what's up with the shawl?
It was pulled off the bargain
wrack at a boutique shop.
I borrowed a sewing machine
and remade it to look
like a brand name.
Home Ec. always was
your best subject, huh?
[NAKAMURA]
All the pieces are in place.
Go get him, Professor Bitch!
[IRINA] This shawl. It wouldn't
stand a chance in high society.
And this amateurish
table setting.
Worlds apart from the posh
restaurants I frequent
in the line of duty.
Ha! And don't get me started
on the lack of privacy.
[IRINA]
Still.
It's fun! Who would've guessed?
I'm starting to love
those little brats.
I'm gonna do it! I'm gonna
seduce the square! Watch me!
The trip was rough.
So much happened.
But at least we got results.
I didn't count on how,
but I sure got to see
those kids reinforce
their fundamental training.
Optimistically, I think we'll
get him during second term.
Of course, you realize I'm
gonna rely heavily on you.
Something wrong?
[IRINA]
Hey. Karasuma.
Do you know what
it means to kill?
To actually end somone's life?
[IRINA] Got a little
dark there, didn't I?
Your napkin.
It's all bunched
up in your collar.
I really like you, you know.
Well, goodnight.
[IRINA] Ugh! You awkward,
brainless idiot!
You were supposed to talk about
how you feel, not how you kill!
[NAKAMURA]
What kind of half-assed,
G-rated kiss was that?
[IRINA]
Huh?
Come on! I thought grown-ups
use their tongues!
Do not start even start
in on me with that crap!
Being a grown-up is a lot
harder than it looks!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't lose heart, children.
I'm sure she has something
appropriately indecent
in mind for later on, right?
Wrong! Don't say that,
you pervert!
[KARASUMA]
Uh...
[KARASUMA] I'm gonna go
ahead and ignore that.
Duty comes first. Period.
It's second term. Training
is about to get very real.
We have to kill him.
[NAGISA]
And so,
our "assassination vacation"
came to a close.
[KARASUMA]
Wait.
Was she practicing a new
seduction technique?
That was impressive.
[NAGISA]
Before school started back up,
we were all spending
the last days of summer
doing our own thing.
[NAGISA'S FATHER]
How's your mom?
You two getting along okay?
You can't be having that much
fun as strict as she is.
Sorry I'm not around
much anymore.
I wish I could be a better dad.
[NAGISA]
Don't worry about it.
She's not so bad if
you don't tick her off.
[NAGISA'S FATHER]
Is that right?
Y'know the other day, I--
You what? I'm listening.
[NAGISA]
A summer festival?
[KORO-SENSEI]
The last day of summer vacation!
Let's hang out and have some
mindless fun! What do you say?
[KORO-SENSEI]
I thank you.
[NAGISA]
Uh, thanks for the sushi.
[NAGISA'S FATHER]
Whoa. You're already finished?
[NAGISA]
Sorry. I gotta get going.
See ya! Let's do this again
sometime. Take care!
[NAGISA'S FATHER] He's cheered
up since last I saw him.
[KARMA]
Huh.
A summer festival?
[KORO SENSEI]
I just thought of it today!
I asked the whole class,
but almost everyone seems
to have other plans.
I'm starting to feel rejected.
[KARMA]
All right. I'll go.
Eh. It's not like I was doing
anything else, anyway.
[LOVRO]
Festival, you say?
I'm honored my target
would think of inviting me.
But I'm afraid I'm out of
country on business.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Argh!
I'll pick you up!
It's no trouble!
Please! Mr. Karasuma's in a
meeting! You're my last hope!
If you don't come,
no one will be there!
[LOVRO] Don't be
ridiculous. I'm working.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes, yes.
Well, feel free to pop by
and kill me anytime.
I will, thanks.
[LOVRO]
According to Karasuma,
our young friend pulled off
the secret move I taught him
as though to the manner born.
Indeed. Every country
has its Natural.
It's rather a shame I couldn't
bring him with me.
[grunts]
[YOUNG MAN]
From the day you were born,
from your first breath,
I've been beside you.
[YOUNG MAN] Be not afraid.
Fear not the name of the Reaper.
[HINANO]
And I got a super great deal!
[TOKA]
Yeah you did!
[chuckling]
[KANZAKI]
It's so fizzy!
[KORO-SENSEI] Excellent! Quite
a few more of you showed up
than I'd been led to expect.
In the event that no
one bothered to come,
I was contemplating seppuku.
Oh. Guess we really shouldn't
have showed up, huh?
[RYUNOSUKE, HAYAMI sigh]
[NAGISA] Chiba? Hayami?
Why are you guys so depressed?
We both got banned from
the shooting gallery.
It was so easy we
sorta got carried away.
--We needed the practice.
--[KARMA] Hey, mister.
So far I've only scored
as high as fifth place
on any of your games.
Seeing as that drives
down the probability
of winning fourth
place or above to,
hold on, let me give
you a concrete figure.
Hey, how 'bout that? 0.05.
I was wondering if the prizes
are worth what I've spent.
I mean, if you
don't trust my math,
we could always ask a cop.
All right, I get it.
You can have your money
back. Just keep quiet.
[KARMA]
Oh, I don't think so.
I didn't blow my cash
to get a refund.
I want that game console.
[NAGISA]
Karma sure is persistent.
[OKAJIMA]
He knew that guy was a cheap
before he even started playing.
[MAEHARA]
Ooh.
Seriously, man, is there
anything you can't do,
or are you just that
freakin' awesome?
It's all in the wrist.
You've gotta flick like you
would if you were holding knife.
That oughta do it.
Okay, good haul.
See, this is how you make a
feast when you're dirt poor.
I hear ya'.
Should I pan fry
them or go sashimi?
[MAEHARA]
Wait. That's his dinner?
[KAEDE]
Wow. Everybody's raking it in.
Yeah.
Turns out assassination
skills come in handy
in the everyday world.
[KAEDE] Like getting all the men
in the Chamber of Commerce tent
to buy you drinks?
I can see that.
[NAGISA]
Where's Koro-sensei?
Being entrepreneurial.
End of the month.
He's strapped for cash.
[NAGISA]
Huh?
The food stalls? Really?
[KAEDE] Only one at first,
but he branched out.
Started setting up in the
stalls that closed early
after they sold out
of all their stuff.
[NAGISA]
Uh-huh.
So basically he's taking
advantage of all the stalls
we put out of business.
Of course.
[HINANO]
Awesome!
[MAEHARA]
Cool!
[ISOGAI]
Gorgeous.
What a vacation, huh?
Sure was packed.
[NAGISA]
Mh-hm.
But something tells me
our second term's gonna
be even more packed.
So, the reward stands.
If he's not killed by
more than one person.
Given what we know transpired
over the summer break,
however, it's wise to
anticipate a group effort.
The children did have
him fairly cornered.
They seem to work
well as a unit.
If they succeed as a unit,
the reward will be tripled.
[NAGISA]
However it all plays out,
when this class is over,
none of us will be who
we were when it started.
[KAEDE chuckles]
[NAGISA]
And like most things in life,
this term will have
its ups and downs.