[VOICE ON PHONE]
Isn't that a shame?
I can't see them all
from this angle.
Ah, well. A cross-section of
the agonized will have to do.
I ought to poison kids
more often. [chuckles]
Maybe when this is over
I'll invest the reward money
in a steady supply of
fresh-faced runaways.
[foot steps]
[GASTRO]
Fourteen. No, wait.
Fifteen total.
And young. Mid-teens
or thereabouts.
You can tell by their breathing.
Everyone not laid up
with the virus is here.
[gun shot]
[OKANO, FUWA whimper]
[GASTRO] FYI, this room
in completely soundproof.
You'll all be Swiss
cheese long before
anyone comes to the rescue.
Come on, we all know you ain't
got the grapes for homicide.
Surrender like good
li'l boys and girls
and we'll go see the Big Guy--
[HAYAMI] Damn it! I was
aiming for his gun.
[GASTRO] What the hell?
They've got live ammo?
That's the sound of one
of our boys' M-Sixties!
These aren't just
junior high kids.
They're trained assassins.
Delicious.
[ISOGAI grunts]
[TOKA]
Ah!
[GASTRO]
This is shaping up to be a job
I can really sink my teeth into!
[GASTRO laughs]
--[STUDENTS grunt]
--[NAGISA] It's too bright!
[RYUNOSUKE]
Those backlights are blinding!
[GASTRO] This is gonna
be like a four-star,
--kill-n'-cook free for all!
--[gun shot]
[HAYAMI gasps] How'd he fire
through such a small gap?
[GASTRO] I never forget
an enemy's position
once they've fired.
Acquired that trick in the army.
Think of it as
battlefield synesthesia.
I can echo-locate the source
of hostile gunfire with
pinpoint accuracy and
check my own gun by taste.
Now, then. Heh.
I know there's one more
stolen firearm out there.
[KORO-SENSEI] Standby,
Hayami! Hold your position!
Wise decision not to fire,
Chiba. Well played.
Our opponent doesn't
have a lock on you yet.
[KORO-SENSEI] Hang tight
and wait for my signal.
I'll keep an eye on him and tell
you when it's time to shoot.
[GASTRO grunts]
Where is that coming from?
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[GASTRO] Hey! You in the
front row! Don't stare at me!
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
A seasoned marksman
versus adolescent assassins.
Our modest advantage will,
I think, be quite enough.
Okay, Kimura!
Run five seats to your left!
Terasaka and Yoshida!
Dash three seats to either side!
We've made a blind spot!
Kayano, two rows forward
into the gap! Go!
Karma and Fuwa, move
eight seats right!
Isogai! Five seats left!
[GASTRO grunts] Idiot.
He's shuffling them all up.
Big mistake. Now I know their
positions and their names.
Verbatim memory, pal.
[KORO-SENSEI] Alternate
naming scheme: Student Twelve!
Move right and
continuing prepping!
Students Four and Five,
train your camera on the
target from between the seats!
Use Ritsu to keep Chiba apprised
of his movements onstage!
[KORO-SENSEI] Ponytail,
shift position to front-left!
Motorcycle Fan, you as
well: two seats down!
The student who checked out
Takebayashi's favorite maid cafe
only to discover
he kinda liked it,
discombobulate the target
by kicking up a racket!
You rat-bastard,
that's nobody's business but
mine! How'd you even know?
[GASTRO] Who's who?
Where are they? I can't...!
[KORO-SENSEI]
All right, Chiba.
The moment of truth is upon us.
Get your bearings, my boy.
When I give the command,
fire at will!
[GASTRO]
Crap. Where is he?
[KORO-SENSEI] Hayami,
you're on follow-up as needed.
Focus on blocking the enemy's
evasive maneuvers.
Now, a word of advice to our
cool-headed sharpshooters
who flubbed the assassination
attempt earlier today.
[RYUNOSUKE gasps]
[HAYAMI gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Don't let one
failure overshadow the skills
you've worked so
hard to cultivate.
The best of us fall short of our
abilities from time to time.
You maintain a facade
of stoic nonchalance,
but feel burdened by the
confidence your classmates place
in you all the same. Few
guess at your inner anguish,
but it's there just
beneath the surface.
[HAYAMI'S MOTHER]
You're alarmingly calm
for someone with these
grades, young lady!
Or should I have known better
than to expect you to care?
[RYUNOSUKE'S MOTHER]
He won't explain himself.
It's like he can't be bothered.
I don't know my own son anymore!
[KORO-SENSEI]
You're not alone in this.
You give it a brave face,
but you needn't bear
the pressure on your own.
If you miss the shot,
there's a fallback strategy.
We'll play hot
potato with the gun
and continue shuffling
everyone until our foe
has no idea where the
next shot will come from.
The reason that
strategy will work
is because everyone here has
tasted the agony of defeat.
Yes, there's pressure. But your
classmates are in the same boat.
Learn to take solace in that.
[GASTRO]
Thanks for the pep-talk.
Gave me time to get my bearings
and work out a counter-strategy.
Everybody's moved
except Student Twelve.
And I have a pretty
good idea where they are.
They're all breathing
heavy, though.
Like they're nervous,
cookin' something up.
Meh. Doesn't matter.
The second someone pops
they're li'l head up, they die.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey-dokey! Here we go!
[GASTRO]
Oh, yes.
The flavor. I am
one with my gun!
[KORO-SENSEI] Student Twelve!
Stand and fire, now!
[GASTRO]
A-ha!
A decoy?
[RITSU]
That's where you want to aim.
[RYUNOSUKE]
You got it.
[GASTRO laughs]
Nice shootin' there, son.
Too bad. Now I know wher--
[grunts]
[GASTRO] Th-They aimed for the
brackets on the stage lights!
That's not fair!
[HAYAMI]
Finally.
[GASTRO groaning]
[TERASAKA]
Tag 'im and bag 'im!
[SUGAYA sighs] I'll just make
a scarecrow in total silence.
No big.
That was a white-knuckle ride.
I'm impressed they
held it together.
I've known pros who
would've tanked.
[KORO-SENSEI] With a balance
of opportunity and motivation,
anyone can expand
their horizon.
They just have to move out
of their comfort zone.
But we can't often
do so on our own.
We need a foe to challenge
our complacency,
force us to draw upon resources
we never knew we had.
That, you see, is precisely
why I became a teacher.
To spark potential.
To give my students both
the opportunity to succeed,
and the motivation.
[KARASUMA]
Some education. Look at 'em.
These kids've just come
through a shoot-out.
[HAYAMI, RYUNOSUKE]
Uh?
[RYUNOSUKE, HAYAMI laugh]
[KARASUMA] And here they are.
All smiles and self-confidence.
[BODYGUARD A groaning]
That's not bad.
Looks like a good portion
of my mobility's back.
I think I'm up to
about half-strength.
Which means you're
about twice as badass
as an average human being.
[MEG] Why didn't we just send
him on this mission alone?
[NAGISA] That'll lead us
to the top floor, right?
[KAEDE]
Yep.
We're seriously coming
down to the wire.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Children!
[STUDENTS]
Uh?
[KORO-SENSEI] It occurs to me
the mastermind waiting for us
above is not attuned
to his resources.
In fact, thus far
his hired hands
have been egregiously misused.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Lookouts? Glorified bouncers?
This isn't how one
employs assassins.
If our foe had aligned
the men we've encountered
with their skill set, they'd
have been fearsome indeed.
You've got a point.
The last guy wasn't off target
by so much as a centimeter.
[KORO-SENSEI]
And consider Karma's opponent.
Normally, the man would've
simply snuck up behind him
and crushed his windpipe
before we even knew
of his existence.
[KARMA]
No doubt. Sure.
[KARASUMA] Of course.
Why didn't I see it before?
The mastermind doesn't
think like an assassin
because he isn't one.
[KARASUMA]
All right. New plan.
First off: Isogai, Terasaka,
Yoshida, I want...
[TERASAKA]
What's your deal?
[NAGISA] Dude, you're
seriously burning up.
You feeling okay? Wait...!
[TERASAKA]
Shut up! I'm fine. Look, man.
I've got stamina to spare.
It's just a fever.
My system will kick it out.
But the virus is deadly!
Damn it, Mr. K almost
died 'cause of me!
If I hadn't been an idiot,
he wouldn't have gotten gassed.
And in case you haven't
been keepin' score,
that's not the first
crap I've pulled that
nearly cost every
one their lives.
If I drop out, I'll
bring the mission down.
Who cares if I'm sick?
I'm not gonna do that!
Terasaka, don't!
[TERASAKA]
Watch me.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ooh, namba!
Ninjas are said to have
used this walking style.
I've noticed my students favor
the silent, thoughtful approach
to killing these days over
the more abrupt methods.
Look at them now.
Despite the time crunch, they
stubbornly refuse to panic.
I'm so indescribably proud!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whoever we're about to face,
my students will certainly
give them more
than they bargained for!
[KARASUMA] Odds are the
antidote's in the case.
And that the case is rigged
with plastic explosives.
[KARASUMA]
We're right on time.
Ideally we'll be able to
take this guy by surprise.
If he spots us, his
first instinct will be
to go for the detonator.
I'll take it upon myself
to shoot him in the arm.
Once that's out of the way,
we'll rush in as a group and
dog-pile the son of a bitch.
[KARASUMA]
Now!
[TAKAOKA]
Ugh. This itch.
[NAGISA]
Uh.
[TERASAKA, YOSHIDA]
[OKANO, ISOGAI gasp]
It burns no matter what I do.
Still, one man's sensitivity is
another man's hyper-vigilance.
Makes me feel wired
to my surroundings.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[TAKAOKA] You didn't think
this'd be easy, did you?
I told you I'd find a
way to wipe the octopus
off the face of the earth.
Oh, and as you can see,
when it comes to little details
like detonator switches.
I'm a big believer
in redundancy.
[NAGISA]
We'd heard that voice before.
Only now, it sounds even more
sinister than I remember.
[KARASUMA] I reached out to four
professionals before we came
on this trip. Three of
'em freelance killers.
But, the other was an old
colleague, who, it turns out,
went MIA after embezzling funds
from the Ministry of Defense.
What in the hell do you think
you're doing? Damn it, Takaoka!
What naughty children! Trying
to sneak up on dear ol' dad.
You disappoint me. I thought
I raised you better than that.
I know some boys and girls
that are going to have
to go to summer school.
[KIMURA, MEG, KAEDE gasp]
[NAGISA] Mr. Takaoka.
Buy... how could you?
[TAKAOKA] Let's head
up to the roof, huh?
I've got a little
surprise up there
you're bound to
get a kick out of.
Oh, and before you
get any bright ideas,
bear in mind you're
only alive because
daddy's feeling generous.
[KARASUMA]
Hiring assassins,
infecting students with a
potentially lethal virus.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Are you out of your mind?
Strong words, there friend.
I assure you I'm perfectly sane.
Though, I suspect world-saviors
are often thought of as mad.
If you had done as I instructed
and had the runts of the litter
bring the goods on their own,
my assassination plot would've
gone off without a hitch
and we'd all be winners.
I'd wanted to use
what's-her-name.
Kayano? Yeah.
She was integral to the plot.
Oh-ho, and it was a doozy!
The bathtub in my suite
here is overflowing
with anti-Sensei BB's.
I'd've set her up in
there with the target
then entomb the whole
setup in concrete.
The only way for the octopus
to return to his normal form
without touching the
BB's would've been
to blow everything sky-high,
including the girl.
We all know he'd never
do such an inhuman thing
to the children in his care!
So, I figured he'd take
the honorable way out
and opt to dissolve
in lieu of killing one
of his students!
[STUDENTS whimper]
[STUDENTS growl]
He's a monster!
[TAKAOKA] I won't lie, it
gave daddy quite a fright
when he saw you'd
all come en masse.
Doesn't change things
much, but still.
Oh, and my mood will
play a significant role
as to whether you
walk out of this alive.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Intolerable.
You can't really imagine
you'll get away with this.
[TAKAOKA] Actually, I think
there's a pretty decent chance.
Either way, I believe we
can all agree this route's
a hell of a lot more humane
than the treatment I
got from your class!
[COLLEAGUE A]
Did you hear?
Takaoka got his ass handed to
him by a class of junior kids.
[COLLEAGUE B] He blew his
mission after he bragged
about his teaching chops?
Oh, man. That's hilarious.
[COLLEAGUE C]
The higher-ups'll think twice
before they give him
another assignment.
[TAKAOKA]
Now, every time I catch people
lookin' at me sideways.
Every time I think of how you
bluffed me with my own knife,
my skin itches so badly I can't
sleep through the night!
I hope you're proud
boys and girls,
because you've condemned
daddy to hell!
Negative evaluations,
demotions, gossip.
You have no idea what it's
like! My future is gone.
You specifically,
Nagisa, must answer
for the grave injustice
done to my reputation!
I get it, he asked for the
shortest students to come
because he knew Nagisa
would be one of them.
Nagisa had every right
to do what he did to you!
I see.
So this actually has a lot more
to do with you settling a score
than anyone saving the
world. Think about it.
Is beating up a kid gonna
repair your self-esteem?
Wouldn't someone my size
be more interesting?
[TERASAKA]
Look, you crazy son of a bitch.
Nagisa kicked your ass
by your own rules,
so you've got no one
to blame but yourself!
And here's the deal.
Even if you'd won,
we'd still despise you!
Nothing you could've done
would've changed our minds!
I don't remember asking
for your opinion!
Love me or hate me, maggots.
I'm the guy that can take
half of you out right now
with the push of a button!
Heh. You, Short Round.
Let's go up to heliport.
Just you and me.
Don't do it, Nagisa! You
don't have to listen to him!
[NAGISA]
I don't want to. But I'm gonna.
[TAKAOKA] Get a move on!
Pick up the pace!
I'm afraid what'll happen
if I don't do what he says.
I'll play along for now and see
if I can talk some
sense into him.
If he calms down, maybe
he'll give us the antidote.
Please be careful, Nagisa.
[KAEDE] I don't like
where this is going.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
Don't even!
[TAKAOKA] Stay right
where you are, tough guy.
Don't take this
the wrong way,
but I don't trust you not
to throw a monkey wrench
into my alone time Nagisa.
[NAGISA gasps]
[STUDENTS, KARASUMA gasp]
[STUDENTS, KARASUMA gasping]
[TAKAOKA] There we go. Now
it's just you and me, kiddo.
You understand where I'm
going with this, right?
[NAGISA]
Uh!
[TAKAOKA] Revenge is an ugly
word, but if the shoe fits.
You've got it wrong,
Mr. Takaoka.
I didn't come here
to relive our fight.
[TAKAOKA]
Course not.
You don't have the element of
surprise on your side this time.
There's not a thing
up your sleeve
to keep me from killing you.
[TAKAOKA]
Thing is, it'd be over too fast
if I went at you full
bore right off the bat.
I want to savor this, so
here's what I need from you.
[NAGISA]
Uh...
[STUDENTS gasp]
[TAKAOKA] Get on your hands
and knees... and apologize.
Say you're sorry for
pulling a cheap trick.
Admit you relied on
the ol' bait-and-swith
to cover lack of skill.
I'm, sorry.
I don't believe you!
Kneel down lower,
you little worm!
I wanna see your forehead
touch the ground
like the sole of a boot!
[NAGISA] I'm sorry for pulling
a cheap trick on you.
I just did it to cover up my
lack of skill. I'm very sorry.
[STUDENTS, KARASUMA whimper]
Not bad. Now apologize
for essentially asking me
to hit the road afterwards.
Good gracious, the audacity!
All the trouble I went
through for you kids,
and that's how you talk to me?
I'm entitled to respect
for the sacrifices I made!
I was wrong to treat you that
way. You deserve respect.
I am truly, deeply sorry.
Please find it in your heart
to forgive me. I was wrong.
[laughs] I'm starting
to believe you.
Daddy feels much better.
Was that so hard?
You know what this needs,
to help the lesson sink in?
Pictures of people who've died
from the virus I infected
your buddies with.
Smog let me borrow a few
from his collection.
The effects are spectacular!
Boils over every inch
of their bodies,
faces like a bunch of grapes.
You'd get a laugh out of
that, wouldn't you kid?
[NAGISA gasps]
Please, no!
[KARASUMA gasps]
[TERASAKA gasps]
--[KIMURA whimpers]
--[OKANO gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[TAKAOKA laughing]
Yes! That's the face
I wanted to see!
You know, you should
make a scrapbook
of this vacation including
pictures of your friends dying!
You could call it Nagisa's
Book of Boiled Over Faces!
[TAKAOKA laughs]
[NAGISA panting]
[KARASUMA gasps]
[STUDENTS gasping]
Kill you.
That's right. That's
the way, sonny boy.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, dear.
I'll kill you!