[SUGINO sighs]
[SUGINO] The crappy
weather's finally over!
It's gonna get hot soon.
Let's start spending
more time outside.
I wanna be more active.
Sounds good. You know I'm game.
What would the two of you
say to some fishing?
Fishing? That sounds like
it'd fun. What's in season?
In the Summer months,
delinquents are out in droves.
Use Nagisa as bait,
and there's no limit
to how many of the bastards
we can shake down.
[NAGISA] I didn't realize
delinquents had a "season."
[SUGINO] Seriously,
though, let's do something.
[NAGISA]
There's always the beach.
[STUDENT B]
Play hard today!
[KARMA]
Hm?
[PLAYER A]
Good one, capt'n! Nice throw!
[SHINDO]
Hey, hey! Look who it is!
Long time no see, Sugino!
[PLAYER B]
Whoa!
--[PLAYER A] Check it out, guys!
--[PLAYER C] Sugino!
[SUGINO]
Hey!
[CLUB MEMBER D]
'Sup, dude?
Way to never come by and say
hello to your old teammates.
[SUGINO]
Ha. Yeah, I know. I suck.
[CLUB MEMBER D] You're
pitching in the big tournament
next week, right?
[SUGINO] Well, they
haven't decided on it yet,
but I'd sure like to.
[CLUB MEMBER C]
Man, it'd be epic if you did!
Yeah.
You have no idea how jealous
we are of you, man.
You get to be in E Class
goofin' off all day.
[CLUB MEMBER B]
We've gotta hit the books
and practice like our lives
depended on it. Blows.
[SHINDO]
Hey, c'mon. Be nice.
Don't make such a big deal out
of it. He won't understand.
Burning the candle at both ends
is a privilege of the gifted.
[KARMA]
Humility much?
Wow, sounds to me
like somebody thinks
they're one of the chosen ones.
[SHINDO]
Heh, I am.
You don't believe me? Fine.
See how you feel after
watching me in the tournament.
There's great, then
there's everybody else.
Now guess which one I am.
That's just the way things are.
I don't make the rules.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah-ha!
A friendly, class-versus-class
baseball tournament, eh?
A healthy body promotes
a healthy mind.
Approved! Except, uh...
I note that E Class
isn't included
in the tournament bracket.
They leave us out to keep
things nice and even.
It's hard to have a tournament
with an odd number of teams.
We get to play the exhibition
game at the end, though.
So, there's that.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Exhibition game?
[MIMURA] Yeah. It's a
spectacle, basically.
We get split up by gender,
pitted against the Baseball
and Girl's Basketball Team
while everyone watches.
[KORO-SENSEI] So it's not
exactly a consolation prize.
Nope.
--[chair clatters]
--[KORO-SENSEI grunts]
[TERASAKA] If you dweebs wanna
be a laughingstock, fine.
Me an' the boys got too much
self-respect. We're out.
[ISOGAI] Hey, hold on
a second! You can't just--
Oh, fine.
We should ask Sugino
for some pointers.
He's the baseball guy.
What do you say, man? Any tips?
Not to be negative,
but we're screwed.
Like, royally.
The Kunugigaoka Team has
Shindo as their captain.
Dude can throw a fastball
like nobody's business.
High schools are
already scouting him.
[SUGINO]
It's not even fair.
Not gonna lie, though.
I'd give anything to beat him.
And not just put up
a good fight.
I wanna beat the arrogant
S.O.B. at his own game.
Baseball is my
first love. My life.
It took getting kicked off
the team to understand that.
The odds aren't
in our favor, but--
[KORO-SENSEI] Swing,
battah-battah! Sa-wing, battah!
Oh. Right.
I forgot you don't
need much persuading
when comes to anything baseball.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I've wanted to be the feisty,
no-nonsense coach in a
sports flick since forever!
Don't worry, I won't
push you kids around,
but I brought a table to flip!
[SUGINO] You've put a
lotta thought into this.
[KORO-SENSEI] I've watched
all of you grow more focused
on which direction you'd
like to head in lately,
and it's been marvelous.
Whatever the odds, the name of
the game is always, "Kill! Win!"
And to reward that
fighting spirit,
Coach Koro will
teach you a strategy
guaranteed to
secure our victory!
[ARAKI]
Whoa-oh! It's a high one!
And the center fielder
practically catches it
with his eyes closed!
Game over, folks!
The winner of the Third Year
Baseball Tournament is A Class!
This really blows.
Why do we even play?
I know. The exhibition game
oughta get our minds off it.
Nothing like watching
real losers getting beat.
[TAKADA]
Oh, this is going to be a riot.
[ARAKI] All right. Time
for the exhibition game.
E Class versus the
Kunugigaoka Baseball Team.
Only the chosen ones get
bragging rights, my friend.
Remember that. Victory goes to
the player with the most skill.
On the field, and
in the classroom.
So not a lot of hope for you,
but whatever. Good luck.
Let's play some ball!
[BASEBALL CLUB chears]
[KIMURA]
Holy crap.
Why are they so fired up
all of a sudden?
Even better question:
where's our coach?
Isn't he s'posed to
teach us his "method"?
He's over there.
Mr. Karasuma told him he can't
draw attention to himself,
so he's using forced perspective
to look like a baseball.
He'll signal us with
the color of his face.
[SUGAYA]
Oh, yeah. Real smooth.
[KORO-SENSEI]
One! Two! Three!
So, what did that mean?
[KARMA]
Hiya, teach. Great disguise.
[NAGISA]
"Kill the opposition."
[ISOGAI]
Hmm.
Good advice.
Treat the other team like our
target and we can't go wrong.
This will be excellent practice
for when we finally assassinate
Koro-sensei, right?
Right! Let's do this!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okay, boys and girls.
Let's give our opponents
a taste of what I like to call
Assassination Baseball!
[ARAKI] Okay, folks.
Top of the first inning.
Let's see what the first
pitch has in store!
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
Damn! That pitcher's
throw comes at ya
like a friggin' bullet train!
His top speed is
something like 140.
Whoa! Like kilometers per hour?
That's right up there
with the pros.
Is it me or does it feel
like a crappy away game?
[KORO-SENSEI]
One! Two! Three!
[KIMURA]
Roger that.
Let's go! Hit me!
[ARAKI]
Uh-oh! Nobody say...
Ha. We'll strike out the first
three batters top of the first.
At the bottom we'll get
three runs and it's called.
[SHINDO]
Piece of cake.
[ARAKI] Shindo winds up for his
second pitch, and there it is!
What?
[ARAKI]
A bunt! Unbelievable!
[KORO-SENSEI] Kimura is the
fastest runner in E Class.
Now that our opponents
are caught off guard,
first base is his.
--[KIMURA] Yes!
--[ARAKI] Safe!
--Who saw that coming?
[ARAKI]
E Class has zero outs...
Sneaky little creep.
[ANNOUNCER] Batter number
two: Catcher, Shiota.
[KORO-SENSEI]
One! Two! Three!
[ARAKI]
Holy cow! A push bunt!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ha, ha. They're good,
but they're still just
junior high kids.
Even pros get
discombobulated by bunts.
[ARAKI] But there's nowhere
to throw it! No outs!
Runners on first and second!
[SHINDO]
What the hell?!
I, uh... I don't think I care
for how this game is going.
No way!
This is nuts! You don't bunt
a fastball like Shindo's
and get it to go
where you want it to.
That's not how this works!
So far, so good,
Coach! Nice job.
Practicing against you
really paid off.
[KORO-SENSEI] Pitcher Koro
throws a staggering
300 kilometers an hour!
Infielder Koro sets up
an impregnable barrier
of dopplegängers!
Catcher Koro breaks
your concentration
with expert trash-talk!
[KORO-SENSEI (CATCHER)]
I saw you out behind the school
playing air guitar, Mimura.
Ooh, that fret technique.
[MIMURA]
I can't do this!
[KORO-SENSEI] Now we study
the opposing team's strategies.
To this end, Takebayashi here
has been spying on them
non-stop for the
past three days.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Aren't I the lucky one.
Shindo's pitches top out
at approximately 140.5
kilometers per hour.
He throws curveballs and
fastballs exclusively.
Fastballs 90% of the time.
[SUGINO] He sticks with
what he does best.
At the Junior High Level,
a good fastball is the only
thing you really need.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Precisely!
Which means if we get our
heads around his fastball,
we're in good shape!
So, for the remainder
of practice,
I'll be slowing down
my pitch, considerably,
and imitating
Shindo's form to a T.
Same stance, same force, as if
the boy himself were throwing.
And after dealing with
the pitches I've been
hurtling at you,
Shindo's "fastballs"
should seem like
they're moving in slow motion.
[ARAKI]
And we have another bunt!
[KORO-SENSEI] Furthermore,
we can answer all these pitches
by restricting
ourselves to bunting.
[ARAKI]
Fair ball! Astounding!
It's come to a dead stop
right on the line!
Batter three is safe!
Am I seeing this?
Zero outs and the bases loaded!
A rare off-day for Shindo!
Maybe he's not feeling well.
[ANNOUNCER] Batter number
four: Pitcher, Sugino.
Sugino!
[KORO-SENSEI]
One! Two! Three!
[UMPIRE]
Play ball!
[ARAKI] Shindo readies for
the next pitch, and what's this?
Sugino plans to bunt!
[SHINDO]
Uh. What the--?
Something's not right
about these people.
Are they playing baseball,
or... something else?
[SUGINO]
I know I've got nothing
on the strength of
your throwing arm.
But real strength
is a different story.
It isn't about striking
hard, or often.
[SUGINO] Real strength
is about striking true!
Heads up!
[ARAKI]
He hit it!
The ball is headed deep
into right center field!
I don't believe it!
The runner on first is
following his buddy on second
--and making a dash for home!
--No! This isn't real!
[ARAKI]
And... Sugino, the hitter,
-- lands safely on third!
--[SUGINO] Yeah! That's right!
[ARAKI]
You're not seeing things, folks!
We just had a
base-clearing triple!
This is unprecedented.
E Class has scored...
What the hell's
going on out there?
[ASANO]
You're looking alarmingly pale
this afternoon, Mr. Terai.
It appears you might be
coming down with something.
I recommend you get some rest.
Your team will worry,
and when they worry, it
undermines their playing.
No! I'm fine! Honestly, sir!
Matter of fact,
I've never felt better!
Come, don't be foolish.
You're not well.
That's the only
possible explanation
for this catastrophe.
Faculty members at this
academy do not fail otherwise.
As I suspected, the
poor man has a fever.
Take him to the
infirmary, immediately.
[MANAGER]
Yes, sir!
[ASANO] I'll act as coach
while you recuperate.
Wha--? What are you gonna do?
Do? I think I'll create a
teachable moment about hubris.
Wow. That was a beating.
No worries. There's
always next time, yeah?
It was my fault. My suckage
dragged the whole team down.
Aw, c'mon. That isn't true.
[NAKAMURA]
We all sucked.
t's just, the other team
had huge, jiggly boobs.
Ugh! Made me so mad
I couldn't concentrate.
What on earth is
the deal with you
and your hatred of big boobs?!
[KAEDE]
It's complicated!
Anyways. Let's hope the boys
are doing better than we did.
[SHINDO]
Principal, sir.
We're at the top
of the first inning,
and the final boss
already throws in.
[ARAKI] Ah, okay.
This explain it, folks.
According to a note
I've just been handed,
Coach Terai has
been severely ill
since before the game started.
Apparently, the team is so
concerned about his health,
their hearts haven't
been in the game.
Not one to languish
in the bleachers,
our illustrious principal has
stepped up to take the reins!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER]
Batter number five:
--Second Baseman, Maehara.
--[ARAKI] All right!
--Let's play some ball!
[ARAKI] You've got to wonder
how this is going to-- Wait!
The players are
converging on the infield!
This is highly unusual.
I think it's safe to say
they're on to our bunt strategy.
What the hell, dude? They can't
actually do this, right?
[TAKEBAYASHI] Technically,
if it's in fair territory,
they can defend
however they want.
The umpire could call them
on it if we felt like it,
but he happens to be on their
side. So, fat chance of that.
[ASANO] We must redirect
the game's flow.
Sugino is a formidable talent.
He kept up his skills by
joining a municipal team.
No denying the boy's
making an effort.
But the fact is
neither here nor there.
Everyone makes an effort
in their own way.
What separates you
from the common ilk
is a sense of destiny.
Forge ahead to meet your future,
and rabble like him will
fall in the thousands
before the force
that propels you.
Don't think of this
as merely baseball.
Rather, think of it
as a reconnaissance,
as clearing your path of debris.
Now, do as destiny demands.
[ARAKI]
And he's popped it up!
Maehara is intimidated
by the infielder pressure!
That's one out.
[OKAJIMA]
This is messed up!
How am I s'posed to bunt my way
around a B.S. setup like this?
A little guidance, Coach!
[KORO-SENSEI]
One! Two! Three!
[OKAJIMA]
You mean we've got nothing?!
[UMPIRE]
Strike three! Batter out!
Strike three! Batter is out!
[ARAKI] Bam! Three outs,
one after the other!
The Shindo we all know
and love is back!
Good work, my boy.
Now, keep it up.
Four-seam fastballs are
what will turn the tide.
I want to see high drama.
Throw as if to crush them.
Sir!
And allow me to reiterate.
This is far more
than just a game.
It is a benchmark on
your climb to the top.
[BASEBALL CLUB]
Sir!
[SHINDO]
Let's turn this around!
[BASEBALL CLUB]
Yeah!
[KARASUMA] The man knows how to
light a fire under his students.
Not unlike someone else we know.
Gifted motivator,
photographic memory of faces,
strengths, weaknesses.
Their teaching methods
are one and the same.
And yet, as molders
of young minds,
the two are
diametrically opposed.
They're on a collision course
with each other. I can feel it.
Ah-ha! I think I get it!
So, you hit a ball with a stick.
[ANNOUNCER] Batter number one:
Left Fielder, Hashimoto.
Play!
[ARAKI] Sugino of E Class
throws the first pitch.
[HASHIMOTO]
Huh?
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
[CROWD cheering]
Yeah, Sugino, that's the way!
Don't let 'em get a hit.
None of us can
catch worth a damn.
[chuckles] No worries,
I'm on it.
Shindo, repeat after me.
"My strength is infinite."
"My throw will be a
force to reckon with."
[SHINDO]
"My strength is infinite.
My throw will be a
force to reckon with."
"I will overpower my enemies."
"They will be trampled."
[ARAKI]
No way!
--Two batters struck out
--[KORO-SENSEI] Psst. Karma.
--in a row!
--[KARMA] Huh?
[KARMA] Not the best idea to be
right under my feet, Coach,
'less the object is
to get stepped on.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] You're the first
up to bat next inning, correct?
How about we shake
things up a bit, eh?
[ARAKI] We're at the top
of the second inning
and the invincible bunt defense
is still the order of the day!
[ANNOUNCER] Batter number
eight: Left Fielder, Akabane.
[KARMA]
Hmm.
Move it, kid. Get your tail
--in the batter's box.
--Hang on.
[KARMA] Never pegged you as
the type to play dirty, sir.
If the rules haven't changed,
this little gambit ain't legal.
They're bogarting the infield.
Umpire should've
called 'em on it by now.
Aw, c'mon. Anyone else smell
a rat, or is it just me?
Oh! Nevermind.
You guys are morons.
Baseball's like a foreign
language to you.
[PLAYER F] Quit whining
about every little thing
--and play ball!
--[PLAYER G] What do you care?
[PLAYER G]
This isn't even a real game!
You got a problem,
go cry to momma!
[KARMA] Not sure it's working
like you want, Coach.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's perfectly fine.
The important thing
is to not buckle.
When you see an
injustice, speak out!
[ARAKI] Top of second, and E
Class has given up three outs!
[yelling]
[ARAKI]
A hit! The trajectory is low.
And the ball has smacked
against the fence.
He just missed catching
it off the bounce.
Shindo make it to second
base with time to spare.
We have a double!
[ASANO]
Thank you, Koro-sensei.
E Class sets an example
impossible to ignore.
All the more so for
resorting to cheap tricks.
Between that and genuine skill,
genuine strength, on balance,
which do you imagine
is more inspiring?
Strike, three!
The batter is out!
[ARAKI] Bottom of the third.
The end is nigh!
The real baseball team is on
defense, and then it's over!
Hashimoto, a word.
[HASHIMOT]
Hm? Yes, sir!
Give E Class a taste
of its own medicine.
[NAGISA, SUGINO gasp]
[ARAKI]
A-ho! Lookie there!
The bunters become the
buntees! Quite the twist!
Sorry, my bad.
It's all good.
Don't worry about it.
[ASANO] Imagine my team
bunting against amateurs.
Normally this would
be distasteful.
But... given that the
upstarts are having
their own questionable tactics
turned against them,
we chosen ones
are perfectly justified.
[ARAKI]
Zero outs, bases loaded,
and next up to bat is the
baseball team's pride and joy.
Shindo!
You're mine, Sugino!
You hear? I will crush you!
[ASANO] I've been
building to this moment
since the first inning.
The dénouement will
be precise, dramatic.
This game will be
decided, not by a bunt,
but by the swing of a powerful
young man under my tutelage.
How shall you answer
my move, Koro-sensei?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Karma.
I think it's time to put
your earlier trash talking
to good use.
[KARMA]
Mmm.
Ah. I get it now.
The only thing we can
really do is walk Shindo.
[KARMA] Yo. New marching
orders from Coach.
[ARAKI] And so the
game resumes, except.
Again with the tight
defense positions!
[KARMA]
Choking up the infield
isn't helping the
batter's concentration,
but what are you gonna do?
Now, if the ump had
called you on it earlier,
there'd be a precedent for
telling us to back off.
Ha. You're cool with
this. Right, chief?
[ASANO]
Well played.
But still just another
desperate, undisciplined ploy.
Proceed as you will.
A true athlete does not falter
before such trickery.
Wow. Duly noted.
Heh. We'll hold
you to that, sir.
[CROWD gasping]
[ARAKI]
This.
Uh. I mean, for heaven's sake
they're standing so close!
Talk about point blank range!
Hey, Mr. Chosen One.
Don't worry 'bout us.
You might hit us with your
swing, but we'll be fine.
My, an obvious
attempt at a bluff.
Put everything you've
got into the swing.
Crack a skull if need be.
The penalty will go to E Class
for obstructing the batter.
[SHINDO]
Think you're intimidating me?
Well let's see which
of us pisses themselves
when I brain you
psychotic little freaks!
[UMPIRE]
Strike!
[NAGISA]
Uh.
[PRINCIPAL] They dodged
in the last millisecond.
[KORO-SENSEI] When it comes
to guts and visual acuity,
these boys are
top of their class.
Dodging Shindo's swing
is as simple to them
as bunting his fastball.
[KARMA]
Give us a break.
Holding back ain't
gonna cut it, pal.
On the next throw...
...swing like you're
tryin' to kill us.
[NAGISA]
That's got him pretty shaken up.
He wants to do what
the Principal says,
but can't bring himself to.
Things change quickly
in our world.
One second you're
playing baseball.
The next, something where
the stakes are a lot higher.
[KARMA]
Heads up, Nagisa!
Throw it to third base!
[UMPIRE]
Out!
[SUGINO] Kimura! C'mon,
throw it to first base!
Go for it!
[KIMURA]
Done and done!
[UMPIRE]
Out!
[ARAKI]
Uh-- A triple play!
The game is over.
I can't... This is insane.
The winner is, never
thought I'd say this,
but the winner is E Class!
Well damn, that was
totally pointless.
How did they lose to the?
And to those E Class jerkwads?
All that superior firepower
wasted. What a joke.
[NAGISA] If only people
could see was going on
behind the scenes.
Too bad, really.
This wasn't just a game.
This was a straight-up
battle of wills.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not that anyone's keeping score,
but between this and midterms,
I'd saw we're one, one.
Until final exams,
my good Principal!
[SUGINO]
Shindo!
Sorry, man.
Didn't mean for things
to get so crazy.
For what it's worth, though,
this doesn't change anything.
You're still a better
player than me.
It's one little game.
Don't be so depressed.
One game?
Why'd you go to so much
trouble to win then?
Don't feed me that line;
you wanted to prove you
were stronger and you did.
Take a look at us.
We're not much of a team.
I mean, we all get
along really well,
but collectively we
suck at baseball.
Thing is, though, when
we practiced bunting,
it was awesome.
See, for me, it wasn't
so much about
getting stronger or better.
It was... well...
It was about being proud
of my new friends.
I wanted to show 'em off.
Especially to you guys, y'know?
[SHINDO] This ain't over
between us, Sugino.
The next time we play'll
be in high school.
[SUGINO]
Damn right!
[SUGINPO]
If the Earth hasn't been
blown to smithereens by then.
Somethin' wrong?
[SUGINO]
Uh. Nah.
Just thinkin'.