[KORO-SENSEI]
Hmm...
The moon is all they're talking
about in the States, too.
Does no one care
about anything else?
[SUGINO]
There he is.
Chillin' out back before first
bell, not a care in the world.
Readin' a Hawaiian newspaper
casually picked up
from Hawaii on the way here.
Nice. Good work, Nagisa.
Thanks. I owe ya one
[NAGISA]
Hm. You're welcome.
Best of luck, Sugino.
Heh. Ten billion big,
here I come.
[NAGISA]
We are assassins.
Our target...
...is our teacher.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Top of the morning to you!
[BOTH gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI] It's usually
considered polite to reply.
[gasping]
[NAGISA]
Uh... Yes, sir. Sorry, sir.
Good morning, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
A baseball embedded with
government-issue
anti-me BB's? Creative!
Points for choosing a method of
delivery
quieter than the pop
of a standard air rifle.
Unfortunately...
Once airborne, the weapon
gave me nothing but time.
Ample opportunity, in fact, to
organize a defensive maneuver.
[KORO-SENSEI] A quick visit to
the equipment room, and, ta-da!
I had, pardon the pun,
a handy solution.
[BOTH groan]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Tick-tock, children.
Graduation will be here
before you know it.
Right, then. Homeroom,
if you would please.
[SUGINO sighs]
Yes, sir.
[SUGINO] Damn it. Well,
so much for my fastball.
Big shock there, I guess.
It was a good throw.
[SUGINO sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
"April is the cruelest month,
breeding lilacs
out of the dead land...
[NAGISA]
What are the facts?
This guy vaporized
70% of the moon
and plans to destroy
Earth in March.
He can do it, the issue
is how to stop him.
Oh, and for some reason,
before ending the world,
he wants to teach a bunch of
last-chance
Junior High nobodies.
The Ministry of Defense was
quick to make the most
of the situation.
They gave us a mission:
Kill our teacher,
save the planet.
We're onboard because
the reward money is crazy.
Ten billion crazy.
Hey, hey, Nagisa.
I hear that you
and Sugino's plan
didn't go so well this morning.
[NAGISA]
Hmm... You could say that.
Seems like it's really
bothering him, too.
[SUGINO sighs]
[KAEDE] What's there to get
all bent outta shape about?
I mean, it's not like any of us
could've done better.
[KORO-SENSEI]
...cultural familiarity has...
[NAGISA] The Japanese word for
"unkillable" is "korosenai".
[NAGISA] So we've named our
unkillable teacher...
"Koro-sensei."
[gasps]
Huh...?
[SUGAYA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sugaya!
[KORO-SENSEI] Not a bad
likeness, I'll give you that,
but I'm a little hurt
by the jaw line.
You don't have a jaw!
[school bells chime]
[KORO-SENSEI] That's lunch,
people. If you'll excuse me,
I have some important off-campus
business to attend to.
[ISOGAI]
Tofu from China?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Actually...
I'm catching a ball game
in The Big Apple.
Ciao!
[STUDENTS yell]
He sure knows
how to make an exit.
I know! That thing is startin'
to get on my nerves.
[HINANO]
Talk about unfair.
We're stuck here while
he flies all over the world,
he could at least
bring souvenirs.
[MEG] Think about what he'd
probably bring back:
are you that hard-up
for a mortar shell?
I just sayin' an
exotic snack would be nice.
It's not like he has to
sneak 'em though customs.
You've dedicated a lot of
thought to this.
So, hey, what's
New York's chief export?
I dunno, booze?
Sucks we're not drinking age.
What about something greasy
from one of those food trucks?
[OKAJIMA]
Man! New York girls are hot!
Especially the blondes!
Oh, yeah!
[OKAJIMA] Damn! Can you
imagine if one came back
with him as a transfer student?
[ISOGAI]
Oh. Mr. Karasuma.
Children. Any progress on
killing the tentacled menace?
Define progress.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[KIRARA]
This is E Class, yo.
You gotta lower
your expectations.
All due respect, sir.
He's too quick.
[MIMURA] Like so quick you
can't even see him sometimes.
[OKAJIMA] You said so yourself:
he tops out at Mach Twenty.
How do we kill
something like that?
[KARASUMA]
I don't know.
But you kids had
better figure it out.
Seriously?
[KARASUMA] Seriously.
You're the only hope we've got.
[gasps]
He teaches willingly.
Putting himself in
the line of fire by choice.
[STUDENTS groan]
[CROWD cheers]
[KARASUMA] If we allow that
creature to live,
come March, Earth will be
totally annihilated.
And, in case you need a
reminder of how powerful he is,
take a look at what's
left of our moon.
That'll be our planet in a year.
In short, he's too
dangerous to take lightly.
That's why this classroom
is the last stand
between mankind and extinction.
[NAGISA] If you give a group of
outcasts and misfits like us
a chance to play hero.
Things are gonna get
interesting, to say the least.
Can we do it?
It's a tall order,
especially given everything
we don't know about our target.
We can't even say why
Koro-sensei wants to blow up
the planet in the first place,
let alone what he gets
out of teaching us.
[indistinct chatter]
[SUGINO sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI] There you are.
This may come in handy.
Thank you, Koro-sensei.
Wait, what-what are you eating?
[KORO-SENSEI]
A coconut I grabbed in Hawaii.
Care for bite?
You shouldn't eat the husk.
[KORO-SENSEI] Solid throw
yesterday, by the way.
Hah. Yeah, right.
Says the guy who could probably
throw a ball faster and farther
on accident than I'll
ever be able to on purpose.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Are you on a team?
I used to be.
[KORO-SENSEI]
And you're not any longer?
They, uh...
They kicked me off.
Teams are only for
D Class and above.
We're here to get
our grades back on track.
Extra-curricular stuff
like sports isn't allowed.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sounds suspiciously
like discrimination.
[SUGINO] I'd have
gotten booted either way.
C'mon. You saw my pitch.
I'm too slow.
I never struck anyone out,
wound up bench-warming
most of the season.
I was so depressed I got
just as slow hittin' the books.
That's why I got packed off
here to the mountain.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sugino?
[SUGINO]
Hm?
[KORO-SENSEI] May I give you a
friendly piece of advice?
Need to make sure
these get turned in.
[NAGISA]
That's weird.
What do they have to talk about?
Holy crap. He's ticked off
he tried to kill him!
[gasps] And now he's
literally up in arms!
Please, sir! Don't do this!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Huh?
He was just doing
what he had to!
The deal was you couldn't
hurt any of us!
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
There it is.
I thought I recognized
that pitch style.
You were imitating
major-league pitcher Arita.
[SUGINO gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] That's right.
These tentacles don't lie.
[KORO-SENSEI] Your shoulders
are significantly less
flexible than your
idol's, I'm afraid.
What exactly are
you trying say?
[KORO-SENSEI]
That the famous Arita fastball
that you were trying
so hard to copy...
...is simply never
going to be your thing.
[SUGINO gasps]
[NAGISA gasps]
That's not fair.
You don't know. How could you?
That's ridiculous.
You can't just...
Look, don't worry about it.
[NAGISA]
I get it, why even bother?
Hey, we're just E Class, right?
We're just a bunch of losers
and lost causes!
[sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
You misunderstand me.
I base this entirely on
firsthand experience.
First-through-eighth-hand
experience!
[BOTH]
What is wrong with you?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I even got his autograph!
[NAGISA] You actually
asked him for an autograph?
After you assaulted him?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Unbelievable, right?
--He was so nice about it!
--[SUGINO] He's right, though.
--I almost died!
--Some of us are born
with talent,
some of us not so much.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Talent is relative.
Arita's wrists and elbows
aren't as flexible as yours.
Like I said, these
tentacles don't lie.
Given enough time and practice,
you could become just as
good a player, if not better.
And besides, why settle
for being an imitation?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Next time,
try assassinating me
in your own style.
[SUGINO]
More flexible, huh?
I never realized.
[SUGINO]
How 'bout that.
My own style.
[NAGISA]
Excuse me, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hm?
Did you really fly
all the way to New York
just to give Sugino
a piece of advice?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Why not? I'm his teacher.
Well, it's just that
most teachers I know
wouldn't go that far
for a student,
and I mean, here you are
planning to blow up the planet
by the time we
graduate and all that.
[KORO-SENSEI] Nagisa,
the details aren't important.
Let's just say I'm here
to make good on a promise.
One I don't take lightly.
Ah...
[KORO-SENSEI] The Earth
will be destroyed, yes,
but my first priority is to
you and your classmates.
Nothing beats giving you kids
the credit you're due.
Not even me
blowing up the Earth.
Koro-sensei...
[NAGISA] Could you maybe not
write problems like this
on the back of our tests?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whaa?!
We get it. You're fast.
No point being all
weird about it, right?
[KORO-SENSEI] Aww...
It's only a bonus question...
Honestly, sir, it feels
more like a penalty.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh... Yeah, well...
Anyway, I hope my students
take assassinating me
as seriously as I
take their education.
Not that'll you'll ever
pull it off, of course.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[SUGINO grunts]
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Wow! Nice one!
Broke so fast
I could barely see it!
[laughs]
All in the wrists and elbows,
I'm perfecting a curve ball
that plays to my strengths.
Between that and the
changeup I'm working on,
I've already got a
half-decent arsenal.
Nothing Koro-sensei can't see
comin' from a mile away,
but what are you gonna do?
I'm sticking with it, though.
Perseverance is key...
in baseball and assassination!
[NAGISA] With supersonic speed
and, um, multitasking tentacles,
Koro-sensei definitely
has the advantage.
Killing him won't
be easy. Still...
Can I bother you for a sec?
I wanna take a couple test shots
at you, if that's okay.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
Glutton for disappointment?
[NAGISA] He was such
an awesome motivator.
The kind of mentor who really
knew how to light a fire in you.
We were having,
well, a ball with him.
[MEG]
There he is.
[MAEHARA] Hey. You think that
ice really comes all the way
from the friggin' North Pole?
[MIMURA]
Why not?
He hits up every
other place on the map.
Focus! Think of the
money we're gonna split.
[GROUP]
Koro-sensei!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hmm...?
--[ISOGAI] I hope you brought
--[GROUP laughs]
--enough shaved ice
--for all of us!
--[GROUP laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles] Are the
children opening their hearts
to me at last?
Such beaming smiles!
[GROUP laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Such little savages!
[GROUP grunts]
[coughing]
[KORO-SENSEI] Not the worst
tactic you've tried.
But your smiles were
a bit too forced.
I wasn't born yesterday,
boys and girls.
Now put away these
silly anti-me knives,
and take a moment to stop
and smell, if not the roses,
then these lovely specimens.
Are these from
the flower bed?!
For your information, sir,
we grew these "lovely
specimens" from seeds!
[KORO-SENSEI shrieks]
No kidding?!
[TOKA] Why would you
do something so mean?
We'd been waiting for them to
bloom for months,
--and now they're...
--[KORO-SENSEI] I'm so sorry!
Forgive me, children! Allow me
to, uh, get you fresh bulbs!
[OKANO]
Don't plant them at Mach Twenty!
[KORO-SENSEI]
No, of course not.
[MEG]
Tulips need a delicate touch!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Delicate. Got it.
[MEG]
Stop trying to impress us!
[MAEHARA] He's going to
a lot of trouble for a guy
who's about to
blow up the planet.
[ISOGAI] Yeah, kinda seems
like a conflict of interest.
[OKANO]
Drain the soil properly!
[KORO-SENSEI]
One step at a time!
[MEG] It's probably
too late for them to grow now.
What's with the sea urchin
going all Earth Day on us?
[KAEDE]
Oh hey, Nagisa.
What'cha writing
in your little book?
It's a running list of all the
chinks in Koro-sensei's armor.
A good assassin keeps tabs
on his target's weak spots.
[KAEDE]
Hmm...
Wow. Is that kind of thing
really a weakness?
[NAGISA sighs]
[SUGINO] Nagisa wouldn't
put it in there if it wasn't.
Thank you!
Every detail gives us an edge.
[SUGINO]
"Height: About three meters.
Weight: Lighter than he looks.
Birth date: unknown.
Weak points: Unknown..."
What the hell is this?
Doesn't seem like
a lot to go on.
Maybe not at the moment.
[NAGISA]
The learning curve is steep.
Most classes don't have
murder on the syllabus.
We are the exception.
Then again, we are E Class.
We're the exception, period.
[KARASUMA]
The Ministry of Defense
appreciates your cooperation.
My being brought in
as the new P.E. Teacher
of Class 3-E is
unorthodox, we realize.
But, necessary.
I'll be there
chiefly to observe,
and to offer the
students tactical advice.
My teaching certificate is still
valid, so that's something.
[PRINCIPAL]
You have my blessing, sir.
Just see to it their education
and safety come first.
Thank you for your
time, principal.
[MALE MOD MEMBER A] I figured
we'd meet with more resistance.
[KARASUMA] Hmph. He's being
compensated handsomely
for his trouble.
All this seems rather
convenient if you ask me.
A creature with god-like
powers, untouchable,
beyond the reach of the
military who wants to teach?
Thankfully we've
kept it a secret.
The principal is involved
and the E Class students.
But as far as we can tell,
no other civilians have a clue.
--[TANAKA] I'm gonna die!
--[KARASUMA gasps]
--This is end of the world, man!
--[TAKADA] For you!
Stop screwin' around and
get those grades up, man!
Have you seen
the satellite campus?!
It's a nightmare.
No cafeteria, no food,
bathrooms look like something
out of a horror movie,
the kids are psychos,
the teachers fear
for their lives.
Once you're there,
you're basically done.
Colleges won't touch your
transcript with a ten-foot pole.
[TANAKA]
I know, I know.
Dude, whatever keeps me
outta E Class, I'll do it.
[KUNUDON]
Surprise!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Hooray! It's Kunudon!
Hello, kiddos! That's correct!
It's Kunudon,
your school mascot!
I'm gonna be telling you all
about the sort of
super amazing things we do
here at Kunugigaoka Academy!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Yaaay!
I bet you already know that
we make learning fun,
but I bet you didn't know we're
one of the top-ranked schools
in the country!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Wow! That's amazing!
That's because we emphasize
teamwork and equality!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Hooray! Equality!
Time-tested strategy.
Single out a group as
undesirable and the rest will
fall in line to avoid
being one of them.
Social engineering at its
finest. Very effective.
Makes our job a little easier
than it might be otherwise.
Say what you will, E Class
is ideal for our purposes.
Remote. Secluded.
Full of ticking
teenage time-bombs.
Hey, Mr. Karasuma!
What are you doing here/
New job assignment. As of
tomorrow, I join the faculty
as a P.E. teacher.
Oh, that sounds cool!
It should be fun, yes.
Then I get to call you
Professor Karasuma from now on!
So where exactly is
your target now?
Apologizing.
He messed up
the tulips we planted
so he's reduced his speed
and he's letting us all
take whacks at him.
Is he totally the coolest
teacher ever, or what?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
A few more minutes of this
and all is forgiven, right?
You're a very lucky class,
I'll have you know;
not many teachers would put
themselves in this position.
So, uh, any luck yet?
Uh... No.
This is pretty much
all a game to him.
[sighs] This is not what the
Ministry of Defense has in mind.
Wait, hang on a minute.
There's bound to be a
corresponding weakness.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs] Shoot and
stab to all you want, class!
Even with this handicap,
I am too fast for you!
Only in your dreams
do you have any hope
of getting the deed done--
[ALL groan]
[ALL]
Kill him!
[KORO-SENSEI] Wait, wait, wait!
This isn't part of the deal!
Easy! Oh crap, oh crap,
oh crap, oh crap, oh crap!
Well, your notes are bound to
come in handy at some point.
Right!
That's why I'm jotting
everything down.
[KORO-SENSEI] My tentacles
are all tangled in the ropes!
This isn't what I had in mind!
Stop it, stop it all of you!
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
[OKAJIMA]
Hey, get back down here!
[KORO-SENSEI] Ha-ha!
What's the matter, children?
Can't jump this high?
Oh, wait, of course not!
--[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
--[OKAJIMA growls]
Aw, man! We were so close!
[laughing continues]
[KORO-SENSEI pants, sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI] Guess who's earned
themselves extra homework?
[STUDENTS]
No fair!
[KORO-SENSEI cackles]
[MIMURA] Where's he going?
We're getting closer to a
solution, I can feel it!
Keep this up and it's
only a matter of time
before we got him!
[STUDENTS chatter, laugh, cheer]
[KARASUMA]
A bunch of junior-high kids,
keyed up about killing.
Strangest class ever.
So, whaddaya think?
Do we have a decent chance?
Oh, yeah, no doubt!
'Least I hope so, or it's
gonna be a really awkward
graduation ceremony.
[KARASUMA]
It's a funny thing.
The system's given up on
these kids, and look at 'em.
[ISOGAI]
If we lure him here.
[KARASUMA] They've got
so much positive energy.
So much... purpose.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
[FEMALE MOD MEMBER 2A]
As you can see, our situation
is a desperate one.
Needless to say,
this information is shared in
strictest confidence.
Break the non-disclosure clause,
and you will be subject
to a memory wipe.
[KARMA]
Yikes.
Your fellow classmates
have already been debriefed.
They've done their best,
but so far to no effect.
Once your suspension has ended,
you'll report to E Class
and access the situation.
From there, you are authorized
to proceed as you see fit.
[KARMA]
Whatever.
You expect me to take him
down with this? Seriously?
[FEMALE MOD MEMBER A]
Correct.
That knife, while
harmless to humans,
is designed specifically
with your target in mind.
[KARMA]
Huh. Human. Not human.
Doesn't matter to me.
[KARMA]
Either way, I'm good.
Should still be a lot of fun.
I've always wanted
to kill me a teacher.