[KORO-SENSEI]
Merry Christmas!
[STUDENTS]
[KORO-SENSEI]
What a magical Christmas Eve!
And in February,
no less! How festive!
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Happy New Year!
Out with the old
and in with the new!
That's right, boys and girls!
Throw yourself into study and,
of course, assassination,
with renewed vigor!
Now...
...time to laze the day away.
[STUDENTS]
Where's he going with all this?
Oh, I think I'm starting
to get the picture.
You're trying to cram all the
good times you missed out on
over the Winter Break into
February, is that what this is?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Precisely!
Our only Winter Break together,
and not one of
you came to visit.
'Course, I knew you
were worried about me
and trying your hardest
to find a solution,
which is why it didn't seem
proper to invite anyone over,
but still.
Seems kinda weird to be all
bummed out about it now,
don't'cha think, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI] Water under the
bridge, as far as I'm concerned!
We'll simply reclaim
the time we lost
by having all the fun at once!
[NAGISA] Koro-sensei's
living life to the fullest,
as frantically as ever.
Still. It's February.
March is just around the corner.
We've got to face the future.
Figure out where we're going
before we say goodbye.
Thirty-two days. That's all
the time we have left.
Koro-sensei deadline
is practically here.
[MAEHARA]
Future plans, huh?
Okay, what high
school you goin' to?
I was thinkin'
someplace lower level
so I can have a
little bit of elbowroom.
Well, we've definitely
got fundamentals down
through senior year.
High school can be
about fine-tuning
what Koro-sensei's taught us.
That's one way
to look at it, sure.
I don't know about you,
but I'm gonna push myself.
"It takes a pristine
academic record
to make it in
Communications these days."
So I'm told, at least.
[OKAJIMA, SUGAYA]
Wah-wah!
[FUWA chuckles]
So, Karma, what're
your sights set on?
[KARMA]
Hmm...
I figure I'll just
stay at Kunugigaoka.
You're gonna subject yourself
to the entrance exam
all over again?
Wow, seems kinda low profile.
With your grades you could
get into any school you want.
Put yourself in the shoes
of the kids on Main Campus.
The guy they thought was
exiled is suddenly back,
looming head and
shoulders above 'em all.
What could be sweeter
than sailing by on an ocean
of humiliated faces for
three whole years, right?
That's a winning
personality you've got.
And besides, there are tons
of decent schools out there
if all you care about
is your transcript.
But do any of 'em boast an
arch nemesis worthy of me?
I'm inclined to say no.
Have fun while you can.
Broader ambitions
can come later.
What I want out
of life right now
is a good academic
battle, or three.
That's so you.
And? What's your high
school of choice, Nagisa?
You picked one?
[NAGISA]
Mh-hm.
[NAGISA] Just like Kayano.
Sugino. Everyone.
It's almost time to part ways.
Each of us going
wherever the future leads.
Believe it or not,
my top pick is Keisetsu
University's high school.
It's crazy hard, but hands
down the best shortcut
for getting into the college
Mom hopes I'll go to.
After that? I don't know.
I have certain skills.
There's no question of that.
Trouble is... what I'm good at
puts me out of step with others.
Seems like everyone knows
where they're going but me.
[SAKURA]
Hey. Yoo-hoo!
How many times I gotta
tell you? I'm finished!
Ha, ha. Oh, sorry about that.
Come on, snap out of it already!
You're supposed to be
giving me the academic chops
to march back into school!
I thought the idea was
to enroll this term,
not when I'm like old n' crusty!
Hey, don't worry,
we'll get you there.
Just, dial it back a teensy bit.
[SAKURA]
Huh...
You're worried about your
own future, aren't you?
Junior high kids
sure have it rough.
I have no earthly
idea what I wanna be.
[SAKURA]
Uh?
You have options?
Apart from the obvious
choice of profession, I mean.
Your path seems
pretty clear to me.
What've we been doing
this entire time?
You're gonna be
a teacher, silly.
[NAGISA]
A what?
[SAKURA] Of course, if you're
not feelin' it, I understand...
[NAGISA] It took her saying
it for me to realize.
A teacher. Someone with
the power to change lives.
Suppose a kid gets
saved by a doctor.
Naturally, he grows up
wanting to be one.
A kid sees an assassin
wielding his blade,
and from then on, it's
all he can think about.
Or maybe,
a kid sees a teacher
molding young minds.
Yeah, but...
[EXAMINEE A]
Um, what is that?
[NAGISA]
Uh?
Someone's family, I guess?
[KORO-SENSEIS]
Go! Go! Nagisa!
Go, go Nagisa!
Go, go Nagisa! Woo! Yay!
Okay, then. Um, is that
an actual mob of giants?
Ugh. I do not
appreciate those weirdos
hogging the send-off ceremony.
Koro-sensei, what in the heck
do you think you're doing?!
[KORO-SENSEIS]
I'm cheering you on, of course!
[KORO-SENSEI] You didn't suppose
I'd let my prize student's
big moment slip by unnoticed!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh dear! Look at the time!
I've got to drop by
and cheer on Kimura!
And Kanzaki! And Chiba!
And Hayami! And Hara!
[NAGISA]
Uh!
[KORO-SENSEIS]
You got this! Up, up and away!
[NAGISA] I'll never be a teacher
like him, that's for sure.
[NAGISA] The last career
counseling session
is at the end of February,
after our entrance exams.
I've got until then to make up
my mind one way or the other.
For now, though, I'll focus on
the target right in front of me.
[OKAJIMA whimpering]
[MEG] Okay, I'll just ask.
What's wrong with you, Okajima?
Uh. What, with me? Nothing!
Is it because of the
chocolates? Please.
[OKAJIMA] I-I have absolutely no
idea what you're talking about!
You're sick.
[OKAJIMA]
Uh! It's Valentine's Day!
I'm just excited is all!
And don't worry.
I'm not gonna eat any of that
cheap-o crap you give out!
[MEG] Excuse me? What is
that supposed to mean?
[KARMA]
What do we have here?
[NAKAMURA] And who's the lucky
fella you're giving these to?
What are you talking about?
They're just a formality!
Why do you have to go there?
Everybody likes chocolate.
They could be for anyone!
[KARMA]
Right.
And by "anyone" I assume you
mean this little stud muffin?
[screams]
[KAEDE]
It's true, it's true...
[KARMA] Weird. Her acting chops
are usually more spot on.
[NAKAMURA] Not even
Koro-sensei wised up to her
before it was almost too late.
[KARMA]
It was that kiss.
Ever since Nagisa
laid one on her,
the girl's been a
bona fide hot mess.
[NAKAMURA] Heh. If we bring
the two of 'em together...
[KARMA] ...we can tease two
love birds with one stone!
[NAKAMURA, KARMA]
We've got a shiny new plaything!
[NAKAMURA] His self-esteem
isn't exactly the highest.
Poor guy can't imagine
the opposite sex
wanting anything to do with him.
It's why he's avoiding you.
See, in his mind,
that smooch is something
you're pissed as hell about.
That's just how he is.
Till you say otherwise,
that's what he'll think.
I know, it's just...
I mean, I've played being
in love dozens of times,
but this is totally different.
I have no real-life experience
crushing on a classmate.
Like, what am I supposed to say
when I give the
chocolates to him?
[KARMA]
Ah. Want us to do some recon?
[gasps]
Maybe a little covert
training would be in order?
Absolutely! Absolutely!
[KANZAKI]
I'm, uh, glad you like them.
[KARMA] See, in this case
the receiver is overjoyed.
But observe how the giver is
rather a bit on the cool side.
Total formality.
His "overjoyed" face
is terrifying.
Impressive.
Your shots are just as accurate
when using chocolate ammunition.
Here's the rest.
You've more than earned it.
Good call.
I respect you.
Let's keep it that way.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Sure.
See? Now there's a couple
that's always on target.
Gotta love that skill.
[KAEDE]
I can't imitate that.
I can't even tell
if she meant it.
Gentlemen, I await your
answers with baited breath.
To each of you, a love letter.
I put a lot of
myself into these.
[TERASAKA] Yourself?
More like an ancient curse!
She beat me to the punch.
I had Okuda cook me up a batch
I planned on leaving in
Teresaka's shoe locker.
Here's your
Valentine's Day cyanide!
What is wrong with you?!
That's not what
chocolate is for at all!
[ISOGAI]
Whoa!
All these for me?
Is this for real?
I thought you might
like to share them
with your brother and sister.
Nothing fancy, just bulk stuff
from a wholesale store.
Took me four hours to
ride there and back.
[ISOGAI]
Uh.
But how'd you even--?
When did you study?
[MEG]
It's not a big deal.
After all, I have days
before the entrance exams.
I'm going to state school.
That makes you and
me both, doesn't it?
[ISOGAI]
Guess so. Hope we can get in.
[MEG]
Right?
[NAKAMURA]
See?
Everyone has his or her
distinct approach to this stuff.
Best policy is to say
what you have to say
in your own words.
You should just be yourself.
Yeah. I guess so.
Thank you, guys.
Only problem I see?
[KAEDE]
Hm?
[NAKAMURA]
Privacy.
With the Octo-perv on watch,
there basically is none.
Oh, you can just
leave that to me.
Kayano, I do hope you
brought the you-know-what.
Uh... Oh, yeah.
Oughta put Koro-sensei
on lockdown long enough
for you to get the job done.
Don't worry about him.
Concentrate on giving
Nagisa those chocolates.
[KAEDE]
Right.
Where are my
Valentine's chocolates?
I know I got something!
Nagisa, help me look!
Some joker probably
thought it'd be funny
to hide them on the mountain!
[NAGISA]
Huh?
Kayano?
[NAGISA] What's wrong?
Why're you so quiet?
[KAEDE] Oh, God.
My heart's beating so fast!
How do I do this?
Do I look all right?
What do I say?
[KAEDE]
Uh, hey, Nagisa.
Where're you headed
after graduation?
Honestly, I know the
career path I wanna follow,
I'm just not real sure that
it's something I'm cut out for.
[gasps]
[KAEDE]
He wants to be teacher.
It's obvious he looks
up to Koro-sensei.
Not for the reasons
most of us do,
but because
Koro-sensei has a knack
for bringing out
the best in people.
When Nagisa talks to him
at the end of the month
about a future career,
he'll ask about education.
[NAGISA]
Huh?
[KAEDE gasps]
[NAGISA] What's Koro-sensei
doing up there?
He's fixated, whatever it is.
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Of course he's out of range.
Why would I think he'd leave
himself so open to attack?
[KAEDE]
Oh.
That look. I love it when he
stares dead ahead like that.
He's so intense.
Not that long ago,
revenge was my whole life.
I should've been crushed
when my plan failed,
but I wasn't because it was
Nagisa who stopped me.
He's the kindest soul
I've ever known.
Sure, he's an assassin,
but his bloodlust filled
the hole in my heart.
[KAEDE]
What do I say to that face?
What words do I use?
[KAEDE]
Nagisa.
As a thank you.
These chocolates are yours.
For always being by my side.
[gasps]
[KAEDE]
Here.
Are you sure?
Yep!
--Okay, then.
--But I'm the one...
Mission accomplished.
Job well done.
Move along.
See you tomorrow, okay?
Hope you get in the
school you're aiming for!
[NAGISA]
Yeah, thanks.
[KAEDE] There he goes.
Staring dead ahead.
It's not right for me to get
in his way, he needs to focus.
But I can thank him without
complicating things.
I'll use the sharpest
blade in my repertoire.
My acting ability.
[KARMA] Imagine being able
to cast your feelings aside
at the moment of
truth like that.
Wow, there's no question
she's Miss Yukimura's sister.
[NAKAMURA]
No kidding, right? So noble.
Well damn, now I feel
guilty thinking about
trying to steal from her.
Come again?
Uh, never mind. I didn't
say anything. So, yeah.
[KARMA]
Hm?
[NAKAMURA] What exactly has
Koro-sensei so enthralled?
[KARMA]
Ah. I had Kayano leave a note
and some chocolates
somewhere obvious,
with a special photo of course.
[NAKAMURA]
You dog.
[KARMA] If I'd known it was
gonna work this well,
I'd have used as
bait long before now.
[KARASUMA] A four-star
Valentine's Day dinner?
What's in it for you?
[IRINA chuckles]
I'm told you menfolk
tend to give back
three times as
much on White Day.
Seems like an honorable
tradition to me.
Of course, I can't imagine how
you could possibly measure up.
Ah... We'll see, won't we?
I'm out.
[IRINA] Don't be like that!
At least stay through the meal!
That wasn't meant as a jab
at your manhood, I swear!
You don't know what I went
through to get reservations!
I'm surprised a place like this
would let someone like
you cross the threshold.
[IRINA]
Here, from Hinano.
She asked if I'd
mind passing it on.
You're at school so
seldom these days.
When I see an opening,
that man is mine!
[IRINA]
Poor girl.
She seems to have gotten it in
her head that we're a thing now.
[KARASUMA] Hm. Bet the boys
are brokenhearted.
I got a veritable boatload
of chocolates, even for me.
I'm sure a few kids
thought it might be
their last Valentine's Day.
Can't blame 'em for
going overboard.
So, what's goin' on
in your world lately?
How's the "big plan?"?
[grumbles]
[IRINA] The kids think if
they can keep the Octopus
from blowing up,
everything'll work out.
Of course, we know
better, don't we?
[KARASUMA] That's why
we're in a private room
at a place she trusts.
I should've known.
[KARASUMA]
Maybe.
I have been meaning to
talk to you, actually.
I've been relegated
to providing E-Class
with proprietary guidance,
so I'm kept out of the loop.
They'll likely only brief
me at the 11th hour.
But... something
is in the works.
The government is moving forward
with a secret
assassination project.
There's no doubt.
[EMPLOYEE B gasps]
[EMPLOYEE A] Seeing it again
like this, I'm stunned.
[EMPLOYEE B] But do you
think it can eliminate him?
[EXECUTIVE A] You may take
my word for it, gentlemen.
The question with this weapon
isn't whether it is capable,
but rather how efficiently
and smoothly it can do the job.
[chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI] A first-rate
mind and a first-rate figure!
[chuckling]
--[door opens]
--[KORO-SENSEI yelping]
[ASANO] I must say,
seeing one of my teachers
so enamored with a
questionable photograph
does not strictly
inspire confidence.
[KORO-SENSEI] Mr. Principal,
sir, wherever did you come from?
[ASANO]
I find your work ethic wanting.
There will be a
corresponding pay cut.
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I beg your mercy!
[ASANO]
Miss Yukimura, I believe.
It's a pity we lost such talent.
Her passion for teaching was
matched only by her vitality.
Given a few more years,
she would've become
an outstanding educator.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Indeed.
Oh, by the way,
I understand there's
an excellent chance
of your life being spared.
If you do survive this,
would you indulge me?
I want you to continue
teaching E-Class next year.
Truthfully, I find your fixed
expression and singular anatomy
to be rather, well,
suited to the position.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm flattered, sir.
You judge fellow educators
purely on aptitude,
unmoved by sentiment or
the shadow of their past.
To be offered a job
by such a man
is the best mark
one could hope for.
Alas, I decided it's
best for this year
to be my last at the blackboard.
[ASANO]
What will you do?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Anyone's guess, really.
I have a mind to circumnavigate
the globe in a sailboat.
May I just say how
delightful it's been
having you as an archrival
through all this.
Your dedication is
nothing short of inspiring.
The feeling is mutual.
I don't suppose
you're open to bribery?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh?
[ASANO]
In the grand design,
I rule this institution
from on high
while the Miss Yukimuras of
the world support it from below.
The perfect expression of
my educational philosphy.
[KORO-SENSEI] What's that boy
of yours up to these days?
[ASANO]
Ah.
Arranging the pecking order
for high school, I suspect.
He'll have the whole
system under his thumb
by the end of freshman year.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
A truly remarkable young man.
[ASANO]
Well, we're not quite there yet.
He still has a few
lessons to learn.
[IRINA]
Can I be honest with you?
I'm not so sure it'd
be such a bad thing
if the world were destroyed.
For the kids, anyway.
They'll never get over it
if they can't kill him.
They'll be haunted by that
failure the rest of their lives.
And they'd resent having
their thunder stolen
by some big shot,
government-sponsored mercenary,
or whatever the Powers
That Be are cooking up.
But think about it.
Imagine those kids
watching their teacher die,
the Octopus writhing in agony
at the hands of one
of their classmates.
[IRINA]
They're screwed either way.
The trauma will follow
them to the grave.
However this turns out,
we're talking years of therapy.
Being part of
something like this
just twists you in a way
you can never undo. Ever.
[KARASUMA]
Irina.
[IRINA]
Uh?
Once this business is said
and done, you should quit.
You're just not built for it.
[IRINA]
Excuse me?
[KARASUMA] Can't you see?
Your feelings run too deep.
Over the past year
they've taken the wheel.
If you're this worried about
your students being affected,
what might another job down
the road put you through?
Sure. You can dismiss the life
I've made for myself. Why not?
It's easy to pass judgment
from the nosebleed section.
But here on the ground,
I'm a killer.
There's no going back from that.
No place in the sun
waiting for me
to shed the past
and reinvent myself.
[KARASUMA] Everything we
experience is a tool
for clearing one's path.
That's the most important thing
I've learned on this job.
What those kids taught me.
I understand your concern,
but they have resilience
down to an art form.
Whatever they face,
however horrible,
they know how to let
it nourish them.
Irina, why don't you
come work for us?
Huh?
You have skill,
an impressive range of
professional experience.
As far as we're concerned,
your past is just that.
With us, you'll save more
people than you've killed.
And if you want, every morning,
you can pray for your
victims at the shrine.
Something to consider.
[IRINA]
What do you mean a shrine?
You are aware that I identify
as Christian, right?
And why stay where
I hardly know anyone?
[KARASUMA]
I don't think you understand.
There's no church anywhere
near my house, sorry.
[IRINA]
Uhhh...
[gasps]
What?!
Wait a minute!
Are you saying what
I think you're saying?!
[KARASUMA]
Probably.
[IRINA]
Wah!
A man and a woman can't
live together out of wedlock!
What will people think?!
[KARASUMA]
Suit yourself, then.
[IRINA]
Ah!
No! It's fine!
It's the 21st century!
It's a different world!
Wait for me!