[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey-dokey.
What fiendish assassination
ploy did you have in mind?
First off we'd like you to
enjoy this little video
Mimura put together.
Then high rollers'll cash in
on those seven tentacles.
When you're incapacitated,
that'll be the signal for
everyone else to join.
What'cha think, Koro-Sensei?
Work for you?
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
Splendidly.
We appreciate you
bustin' your butt on this.
Aw, thanks man.
It really came down
to the wire there.
I had to work on the
final edit during dinner.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hm.
A remote locale
completely surrounded
by seawater. The walls and
windows are more than likely
treated with an Anti-me agent.
Outright escape is too risky.
My best bet is to dodge their
attacks within the premises.
[NAGISA]
Sir?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eh?
Um. I'm, gonna have
to pat you down.
Sorry about this, but
we can't take a chance
you have a swimsuit. That'd
sorta put a damper on our plan.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So cautious!
Admirable, but
you needn't worry.
[NAGISA]
He sure is cooperative.
Swimsuit or not,
once things get going,
Koro-Sensei can dodge
us at every turn.
Still, with all of us here,
he'll have his work
cut out for him.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well, children? Shall we begin?
Don't hold back. Come at me
with everything you've got!
Right. Whaddya say, guys?
Let's get to it.
[FEMALE VIDEO VOICE]
AC.
[MIMURA]
Somewhere in Tokyo.
Kunugigaoka Junior High.
Class Three-E.
An average classroom,
except for the teacher,
who is, in fact, a target...
[KORO-SENSEI]
I can hear a few of them
shifting around in
the dark behind me.
A ruse, no doubt, to conceal
that some are leaving.
Alas, boys and girls, I can
establish who's outside
by the relative distance of
their scent. From the direction
of the shore wafts
the unmistakable smell
of our top snipers,
Hayami and Chiba.
[KORO-SENSEI] This video
is exceptionally slick.
You were editor and
narrator, Mimura?
Well done!
Professional-grade camera
work, compelling score.
The viewer is utterly
sucked in--
[MIMURA]
Thanks for tuning in.
Joining us tonight are
two recon specialists
with very intriguing intel.
We'll hear what they
have to tell us after this brief
public service announcement.
When you're a confirmed
porn addict,
bribery's no guarantee
against a scandal.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I gave you popsicles!
[MIMURA] Our subject's
preferred guilty pleasure
is the middle-aged executive.
The sheer size of his
"Cube Farm Cuties Quarterly"
collection is mind-blowing.
[KORO-SENSEI] Blast it,
Okajima! What is this?
--We had an understanding!
--[STUDENTS laugh]
[MIMURA] At a recent
women-only cake buffet,
a questionable attendee loomed.
Eye-witness reports
suggest, you guessed it.
[KORO-SENSEI]
My name is Koroko!
[MIMURA]
Hardly a master of disguise.
We're still not sure
how they exposed him
without realizing
he isn't human.
[KIRARA laughs]
Wow. I've got to hand it to you.
Ironically, it takes balls to
pull off an outfit like that.
[MIMURA] Between paychecks,
our porn addict defrauds
the public to secure
complimentary tissues.
What does he do with them?
The answer might surprise you.
He fries them.
That's right. Fries them.
As if this poor, wretched
educator's dignity
weren't already suspect.
--[MIMURA] And that's not all.
--[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[MIMURA] To truly plumb the
depths of this creature's
depravity, we've prepared a
full hour of shocking footage.
[KORO-SENSEI] There's a
whole hour of this dreck?
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
No point in killing me, class.
I'm already dead.
Emotionally.
Intellectually.
Socially.
Dead.
[MIMURA]
Brutal, right?
But you've got to admit,
it held your attention.
Notice anything strange
while you were watching?
Like, about the venue?
[KORO-SENSEI groaning, gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
What the...?
I couldn't possibly have
missed you flooding this place!
Unless...
...high tide!
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
[TERASAKA]
Weird.
It's like somebody trimmed
down the support pylons.
Seasick, shamed,
and water-logged.
This just isn't shaping
up to be your day.
Everything's conspired
to slow you down.
Right! Time to party, Teach.
Now, you made a promise.
So don't go backin' out.
[KORO-SENSEI]
This is going to be tricky.
But I know precisely
where the snipers are.
I just have to keep an
eye out in that direction.
[RITSU]
Commence operation... now.
Let's go!
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[RITSU]
Time elapsed: five seconds.
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[KARMA laughs]
Did it come apart?
Oh, hell yeah!
[RITSU]
Time elapsed: 35 seconds.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Flyboards?
A hydraulic cage?
Yeah, that's right.
We know a quick change
of environment throws you.
First you're in chapel,
now you're in a cage!
If you're confused, good.
'Cause we'll take anything
that slows your reaction time.
[RITSU]
Fifty-three seconds.
Commencing tactical
volley in five...
four, three, two, one.
Fire!
[ISOGAI]
Careful, guys.
Shoot around him.
Keep him planted.
[MEG] Everybody im to the left
or right by about a meter!
[TERASAKA] Block his escape
with a hail of bullets!
Wait for it.
[NAGISA]
The kill-shot, goes to them.
The ones onshore are decoys
infused with their scent.
He was so focused
on the shoreline,
he didn't see the
hydro-cage coming.
This is how you
snipe a Koro-Sensei!
And, that's game over!
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
Oh, my.
Well played.
[KORO-SENSEI groans, yells]
--[STUDENTS scream]
--[NAGISA groans]
[NAGISA gasps, pants]
[KAEDE]
Nagisa!
[NAGISA] This is totally
different than our
other attempts.
Feels like it worked!
Don't let your guard down!
It's still possible
for him to regenerate!
Right! Isogai,
you and Katakoa go.
Keep an eye out
for the target!
[ISOGAI, MEG]
Yes, sir!
[NAGISA]
We had him!
There's nowhere
he could've gone!
[KAEDE gasps]
Hey, look over there!
[NAGISA]
Uh?
--What is that?
--I dunno.
[TERASAKA growls]
[NAGISA]
Uh.
[KORO-SENSEI laughing]
[NAGISA]
Really?
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
Allow me to introduce my
trump card of trump cards.
My Absolute Defense Form!
[STUDENTS]
Absolute Defense Form?
[KORO-SENSEI] This exterior
coating is comprised
of nano-matrices formed
by surplus energy.
In essence, my body shrinks
down to the size you see now,
and the compressed molecules
create a high density
protective shell around me.
Why "Absolute"?
Because it's
absolutely invincible!
[NAGISA]
Uh...
So, basically you're saying
as long as you're like this,
there's pretty much
nothing we can do.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't fret, my dears.
It doesn't last long.
The crystals comprising this
shell tend to lose integrity
in about a day or so.
Once the bonds break down,
the shell will expand back
into its normal energy form,
and yours truly will
return to full size.
This form is
extraordinarily useful,
but the tradeoff is
complete imobility
for the duration. I can't
propel myself an inch.
This itself carries
its own risk.
Mom! Where did my thing go?
[MOM] It was hideous.
I threw it away.
[BOY]
No!
[KORO-SENSEI] For example, said
immobility would provide anyone
so inclined the perfect
opportunity for launching
me into space.
Something I rather dread.
I've done ample research
into that, however.
Happily, nowhere on this
planet is a rocket capable
of making that
flight in 24 hours.
[NAGISA]
He got us.
All that, and he got us again.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[NAGISA] We exploited every
single one of his weak points.
And still, nothing.
[TERASAKA]
That's crap!
Nothing is invincible if you
whack it hard enough! [grunting]
[KORO-SENSEI]
You're wasting your time.
A nuclear blast wouldn't
leave so much as a scratch.
[KARMA]
Oh, I see.
[TERASAKA]
Huh?
Well I guess that's it,
we're out of options. Huh.
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
You monster!
I can't bury my face in
my hands in this form!
Oh, sorry 'bout that. Let's see
if there's a way to help you
out there. This sea
slug do anything?
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
Anybody know where I can
find a creepy old beach bum?
I'm gonna shove Koro-Sensei
down his pants.
[KORO-SENSEI] No, no, no!
Someone help me, please!
I'd never take that form
with a bunch of kids.
Yeah. Not exactly
his smartest move.
Especially around Karma.
All right, that's enough.
Class dismissed.
For this one,
we'll let HQ decide
the best course of action.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs] Your
superiors will opt to toss me
in a pool of Anti-me liquid,
I'm sure. Good luck with that.
The energy displacement would
explode, as it did earlier.
Everything in the vicinity
will be blown sky high,
including your superiors.
[KARASUMA]
Mm.
[KORO-SENSEI] Still, you should
be proud, boys and girls.
Entire armies the world
over couldn't get as close
to killing me as you've
done tonight.
This was, by far,
the cleverest
assassination attempt
I've ever encountered.
[RYUNOSUKE grunts]
[HAYAMI grunts]
[NAGISA] Sure, he praises our
ingenuity like he always does.
But deep down,
we know we blew it.
This was our best shot.
How do we top this?
Never mind. I don't wanna
even think about it right now.
I need sleep.
Ritsu.
Hi, Ryu.
[RYUNOSUKE]
You recorded it, right?
As faithfully as possible,
utilizing high-speed camera
filters whenever they
seemed appropriate.
Would you like to see?
The second I fired, part of me
knew the bullet wouldn't hit.
It was like... I knew
he couldn't be killed.
I can only be approximate.
The time it took for Koro-Sensei
to adopt his Absolute
Defense Form is unclear.
However, by my calculations,
if your shot had been
point-five seconds faster,
or Hayami's thirty centimeters
to the left, the odds of target
neutralization would have
increased by fifty
percent, at minimum.
[HAYAMI exhales]
[RYUNOSUKE] The whole thing
was so easy in rehearsal.
I was so sure of myself.
I even fired from a less stable
spot at totally nailed it.
But then, when it
was real, I froze.
It's like my fingers got stiff
and my vision went all blurry.
Yeah, same here.
[RYUNOSUKE]
I just...
I caved under the
pressure, you know?
Too much was riding
on me making the shot.
The moment of truth was nothing
like  what we practiced.
I feel like I could
sleep for a month.
[MIMURA] I vote we head back
up to our rooms and crash.
I'm too tired to do anything.
You're just gonna
call it a night?
We did what we were supposed
to, what else do they want?
Granted the octopus
is still kickin',
but we're owed a primo
vacation either way!
Truth, man.
I'm gonna spend all day
tomorrow ogling gorgeous babes!
Just give me a few hours in the
sack, and ladies here I come!
It's all I can do
to keep my head up.
[NAGISA laughs]
[STUDENTS sigh]
[NAGISA]
Something seems off.
I mean, I know we're
all exhausted, but...
Hey, do me a favor. Can I
lean on your for a second?
I feel kinda--
[NAGISA]
Uh! Oh, no, Nakamura!
Oh. Wow. Awkward. Sorry.
I just wanted to go to the room.
Looks like my body
has other ideas, huh?
You're burning up!
[OKAJIMA] Thinkin' about all the
hotties is makin' my nose bleed.
That's new.
--Okajima! Uh!
--[crash]
[KARASUMA]
Uh! What's happening?
Call an ambulance, STAT!
This is an emergency!
It'll take them a
while to get here.
The nearest ER is
on the mainland.
[KARASUMA growls]
--[phone rings]
--[KORO-SENSEI] Huh?
[KARASUMA gasps]
Hey, Teacher Man.
I'd say your students are in
a bad way right about now.
[KARASUMA]
Uh. And who is this?
[KAEDE]
Oh, no! Ritsu!
Take it easy, friend.
There's no need for
you to know who I am.
Just know your squad
of snot-nosed punks
aren't the only ones
tryin' to hit their mark.
You're telling me
you're responsible
for making them sick?
[VOICE ON PHONE chuckles]
You're good.
But they're a hell of
a lot more than sick.
Their bodies are hosting
a lab-manufactured virus.
Incubation period and
specific symptoms vary,
but the end result is the
same. After about a week,
cells begin to rupture and
vital organs become jelly.
[KARASUMA gasps]
[VOICE ON PHONE] The only
known antidote is also lab-made.
Lucky for you, I am
its sole possessor.
Trouble is, I'm lazy.
If you want it, you're gonna
have to come get it yourselves.
There's a hotel on top of
this island's highest peak.
Bring me your precious
cargo, and we'll chat.
[KORO-SENSEI grunts]
[VOICE ON PHONE] Top floor,
within the hour. No tricks.
And because you seem
like the sort of man
I wouldn't want to tangle
with, send proxies.
Two students.
The shortest boy
and shortest girl.
Out of whoever's still
standing, of course.
[KARASUMA whimpers]
[VOICE ON PHONE]
There's a concierge desk across
from the elevators, have them
go there. If all goes well,
you'll have the antidote,
and I'll have the bounty.
Now, this should
go without saying,
but contact outside help
or show up late, and boom.
The antidote goes bye-bye.
The infected die.
[KARASUMA grunts]
[KAEDE, NAGISA whimper]
Hey, you guys were fantastic.
With the target immobilized,
the hard part's done.
I can't thank you enough.
Lady luck is definitely
smiling down on our cause.
--[KARASUMA grunts] Damn it!
--[KORO-SENSEI] Um... Karasuma?
Of all the times for
some psychotic bastard
to sabotage us!
[STUDENTS cough]
[SONOKAWA] Mr. Karasuma, I'm
afraid they're not cooperating.
Even when we play the government
card, the hotel owners maintain
they have the right to protect
their guests' identity.
Naturally.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Intolerable!
[KARASUMA] But not surprising.
The resort our mystery man chose
is a known site for all
manner of illegal operations.
Remote, shady history.
It bares all the trappings of
an ideal rendezvous point.
The owners have connections with
Higher Ups in the government.
Law enforcement knows
to leave it alone.
[sighs] So basically there's
no way of knowing who
the prick is before we meet him.
Ah! Are we really gonna take
this psycho's word for it?
If he's bullshitting us
about the antidote,
we're all gonna die!
Calm down, dude, it's fine.
We came here to be killers,
not victims, remember?
Look how far we've come.
We'll figure this out.
Right. Yeah.
I'll try to stay positive.
[TERASAKA] No way we just do
what the asshole tells us to do.
I mean, come on, use
the runts as a proxy?
Send these two runt
in to close the deal,
and we might as well lay
down a die right now!
[KAEDE, NAGISA growl]
Okay, that was rude.
I'm sorry. I'm just pissed
off that someone's got us
by the balls. And my friend's
lives are in danger?
Forget about it!
We're so gonna die.
I vote we ignore what
the jackass wants us to do!
Let's get everyone
to the hospital
and forget this happened!
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Bad idea.
If we are in fact dealing
with a man-made virus,
a hospital would be
a waste of time.
Not even the most
state of the art ER
is be equipped to handle this.
There's no way for
them to treat everyone.
We'd be dead before they even
figured out what we have.
[TERASAKA]
Seriously?!
[TAKEBAYASHI] I vote we focus
on easing the symptoms for now.
You'd best start heading
to the rendezvous point.
That's the only way, huh?
[NAGISA]
Our hands are tied.
If Koro-Sensei could move,
we might've had a chance.
I'm starting to wish our
assassination attempt
hadn't gone as well as it did.
At the end of the day, this is
all happening because of you.
Gotta wonder if these kids'll
be willing to surrender
their quarry so easily.
[KARASUMA] One hour.
What the hell can we do?
[KORO-SENSEI] I think I
might have a solution.
[KARASUMA]
Uh.
[KAEDE, NAGISA gasp]
Koro-Sensei?
Everything is ready, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent.
Ritsu's finished the prep
work I asked her to do.
If the healthy students
would step closer, please.
Be sure you're wearing something
you don't mind getting dirty.
--[KAEDE] Mm.
--[NAGISA gasps]
[KIMURA gulps]
So high!
--[phone chimes]
--[STUDENTS] Uh?
[RITSU]
I've successfully infiltrated
their network.
These are the proprietary
architectural schematics
of the premises,
complete with guard
post locations.
[RITSU] The highest
concentration of security staff
is stationed in and
around the main entrance,
where it's functionally
impossible to enter
without passing by
the front desk.
However, there is an
alternate point of entry along
the building's side,
just on top of this ledge.
The terrain doesn't permit
easy access, so security,
while present, isn't as strong.
[KORO-SENSEI] You don't want the
madman to have his way, do you?
Courage, children!
Ten of your classmates are ill.
Two others have been left
behind to care for them.
That leaves you to
operate on their behalf.
Sneak in, surprise our
mysterious adversary,
and steal the antidote!
[IRINA]
Irina Jelavich's...
[moans] Super-Secret
Skills Series!
[KORO-SENSEI] Did you know
that Miss Irina can control
her circulation to change
the color of her face?
Red indicates she's drunk.
Blue indicates
feelings of ill health.
All very effective tactics
when going undercover.
But, when she
tried to showcase
this talent, the students
accused her of being
a knock-off of me and her
face went red involuntarily.
[IRINA]
I've been doing this for years!
[NAGISA]
Assassination Classroom!
[IRINA]
Irina Jelavich's...
[moans] Super-Secret
Skills Series.
[KORO-SENSEI] Did you know
Miss Irina can arrange
and assemble an intricate hobby
model in under a minute?
While this does speak volumes
of her kissing technique,
we strongly recommend you not
touch the finished product.
Don't try this at home,
boys and girls!
[NAGISA]
Assassination Classroom.
[IRINA]
Irina Jelavich's... Ah!
Super-Secret Skills Series.
[KORO-SENSEI] Did you know
that Miss Irina is a master of
disguise, able to pass herself
off as practically anyone,
including some of your
favorite characters?