[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes!
Consider this the
Assassination Classroom's
out-of-season research project!
Ground control to Major Tom:
The ISS has been hijacked!
[NAGISA]
With those words,
one of E-Class's most daring
escapades was, well, launched.
[KORO-SENSEI]
"The reentry capsule carrying
the research data will
plunge into the Pacific Ocean.
As a precaution
against potential theft
by the super-creature to
which the said data pertains,
the capsule will remain unopened
while en route to the lab."
An insightful provision
on their part.
I'm not equipped to handle
heavy objects, you see.
A five-ton capsule might as well
be a reinforced bank safe
for all I'd be able to carry it.
[OKANO]
Which is why we'll get them
to show us the goods
before reentry.
Still, though, does Japan
really have the tech
to launch an unmanned
rocket into space?
[KORO-SENSEI]
It's hard to believe,
but as it so happens, yes.
Of course, I might've
had a little something
to do with that,
but it's whatever.
[NAGISA]
There were a lot of unknowns.
A lot to be terrified of.
But when there's a problem
to tackle, we come together.
And when we come
together, blast off.
[ISOGAI]
Okay. We have a plan.
Time to put that
plan into action.
First off, the rocket
only holds two people.
Who's going?
[MALE STUDENTS]
Me!
Huh. 'Kay.
Ah. Wonderful. Boys'll be boys.
[KORO-SENSEI]
This is an experimental vessel
with as yet no
successful flights.
Who's goin' now?
[MALE STUDENTS groan]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I thought so.
[ITONA]
I want to go anyway.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
I love technology. The whole
idea makes my mouth water.
It's just... It's clear
to me who should go.
Nagisa. Karma.
What?
Look, I'm not that fond
of taking big risks,
especially with my
life on the line.
Why don't you send Terasaka
and a dummy instead?
They're both expendable.
Asshole!
Karma the Fighter in
case there's a scuffle,
and Nagisa the Assassin
just to be safe.
That seems like a pretty
ideal hijacking team to me.
Great.
Everyone save up some money
so we can cover the costs.
Don't even think of
skippin' out on this, man!
You nearly killed each other
tryin' to get us all
on the same page!
Be responsible for once in
your life and take charge!
[NAGISA]
Karma?
I say we give it a shot.
What's better than
a trip to outer space
with your best friend?
Eh? Come on!
Sure. Fine.
I did promise to hear
you out, didn't I?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent! Then it's settled.
Whoa! Check it out!
Cool! This where they
do the count down?
[GROUND CONTROL B] Sorry,
ladies. This area's restricted.
[GROUND CONTROL A] Where're
their visitor ID cards?
We're here for a field trip,
but we got kinda lost.
[TOKA] We followed
some random science guy
and wound up in here.
Oops, I guess! Sorry!
Hey, you know...
'Kay, Ritsu, I'm in
the control room now.
You said any of these computers
should do the trick, right?
[RITSU]
Affirmative.
[KIMURA]
Okay.
I'm plugging you in and
getting out of here, stat.
[GROUND CONTROL B]
Hey! Stop tickling me!
[RITSU] Security analysis
complete. All clear.
Installation of
remote control virus
onto the control room mainframe.
Successful.
Both the onboard flight systems
and the ground control network
now operate on my command.
We're good to go.
The first hurdle has
been cleared. Nice.
Hey, Ritsu?
Looks like a big chunk of our
entry root is above ground.
There anything you
can do about that?
[RITSU]
Roger.
And I'm confirming your
current position now.
[RITSU]
There you are.
How 'bout I shut down
the security camera
in that sector for ten seconds?
Sounds good.
[RITSU]
In three, two, one, go!
Security guard passing through.
Next patrol in
approximately ten minutes.
More cameras. Let me
adjust their angle.
There, that should
take care of it.
Please be careful.
[NAGISA]
Will do.
[NAGISA] The staircase to the
rocket hatch is 15 meters,
we'll have to be quick.
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei?
[chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Inspection perfection!
[KARMA] Anyone else
smell a liability suit?
[KORO-SENSEI] Please don't
say things like that!
[RITSU]
All clear.
I'm relaying the pre-recorded
footage of the dummy pilots
in the cockpit.
You can swap them out now.
No one will notice.
All right, Karma. Let's go!
[GROUND CONTROL C]
100, 99, 98, 97, 96, 95,94,
93, 92, 91, 90...
[GROUND CONTROL B]
Liquid oxygen
and liquid nitrogen systems
are functioning normally.
Do you think they'll be okay?
25, 24...
Flight mode, on.
[GROUND CONTROL C]
22, 21, 20, 19.
You know something?
This takes me back.
We've felt this kind of
nervousness before.
Yeah. Definitely.
Except, uh...
...something tells me we've
changed a little since then.
[GROUND CONTROL B]
All systems go.
Main engine ignition.
[GROUND CONTROL]
SRB ignition.
That's liftoff.
[ALL gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ugh! Oh my! It's so fast!
[NAGISA] I didn't realize
you were tagging along!
[KORO-SENSEI] Well,
you know me. I'm a worrier.
Try not to be overly concerned
with getting the
research data, agreed?
You're soaring through space!
Sit back and relish
the experience!
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei.
There's something
I'd like to say.
You never waste an opportunity
to teach us something,
even if you have to
put yourself in danger.
We're very grateful
for that, but...
...your life means more to
us than what it can teach.
It's what this whole
mission is about.
Just wanted you to know that.
[KORO-SENSEI] Thank you.
I do. And I appreciate it.
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
So fast.
[NAGISA]
The escape velocity required
to reach outer space is Mach 23.
Today, for the first time ever,
we were faster than Koro-sensei.
[crying]
[GROUND CONTROL A] Rendezvous
complete. Commence HTV catch.
[ISS GROUND CONTROL A]
Roger.
[GROUND CONTROL A] Mechanical
arm operation verified.
Three more meters.
Two meters. One meter.
[ISS GROUND CONTROL A]
HTV catch, complete.
Commence gripping.
[ISS GROUND CONTROL A]
Demonstration ship,
grip complete.
[ISS ROUND CONTROL A]
Docking complete.
Shield interface, all green.
Air pressure, normal.
Permission granted
to open hatch.
Welcome to the space station.
Your homeland sent you
a new toy to play with.
Why don't'cha get on out
there and welcome it aboard
with a big ol' hug, eh?
[MIZUI]
Roger that.
Hm?
Where's the dummy?
[MIZUI yelps]
[ISS GROUND CONTROL A]
What? Communications are down.
What's going on?
[CREWMAN B]
Huh?
Oh. Hi there!
[KARMA]
Hey! You're Mizui, right?
I've seen you on TV.
What the--?
They didn't say anything
about kids being onboard!
[CREWMAN C]
Somethin' wrong?
Heh, the comm link
with Earth has been cut.
Excellent job. Thanks.
[clears throat]
So we have a bomb.
We wanna keep things
nice and peaceful-like.
Back away please.
Let's talk this out.
It's gettin' a little cramped
in here for my taste, boys.
I vote we move this inside
where there's more elbowroom.
Yeah, that's right. Let's go.
[NAGISA]
Okay, so,
all we're after is a copy of the
American team's research data.
That's it.
You have my word we won't be
making any other demands.
[KARMA]
You probably already know this,
but our teacher is the
monster you're studying.
No telling what
he'll do to the planet
if you refuse what
we're asking for.
He's capable of anything.
[KARMA] Okay. These fellas
got calm in a hurry.
I guess that's a career
astronaut for ya.
Well, first of all let me give
you kids a big round of applause
for the balls it
took to get this far.
Uh, thank you, I guess?
But, really,
you can't seriously think
we're that easy to take out.
We're not gonna drop to
our knees over a bomb.
Think about it.
We're astronauts.
We came up here
knowing full well
that death is an
occupational hazard.
[CREWMAN A]
Hm.
What'd'ya say we
put down the weapons?
We're willing to talk this
out like civilized people.
But first, you kids
let our crew mate go.
This is nuts.
Even if you do steal the data,
how do you plan on getting home?
You gonna ask the guys you just
threatened to give ya a lift?
We can manage on our own.
Our classmate worked out
the return-orbit calculations
to the last decimal point.
Yep!
So there's that. And of
course our teacher can do
whatever fine-tuning
we need from midair.
That's incredibly reckless!
Is this fun for you?
We all think we're invincible
when we're young, but damn.
[KARMA] Look, pal, I'm not
here 'cause I wanna be.
Uh-uh. I'm here 'cause
my friend asked me.
Seriously?
[KARMA]
We know we're not invincible.
We've actually given it a lot
of thought the last few months.
Look at us.
We're a bunch of kids prepared
to assassinate our teacher.
That puts us in a
unique position.
We understand how
fragile life is.
Just like you, am I right?
[CREWMAN A] You put a lotta
stock in the harebrained schemes
your target cooks up, huh?
Well, boy,
guess I'll take it upon myself
to accept your demands.
We'll let them see the files.
[CREWMAN D]
Huh?
In exchange,
you can earn those files by
helping us unload our supplies.
Let's put these kids to work
so they can get what
they need and go.
[NAGISA] In the end,
more than anything else,
I think the crew
just wanted to give
a couple of junior high kids
the experience of a lifetime.
This might actually
save his butt.
Maybe, yeah.
[KARMA] That'd be enough
for you, wouldn't it?
What's that s'posed to mean?
Eh, I'm not goin' against
the class's decision
to save him or anything.
Your side won, fair and square.
I'm just curious if
that's what he wants.
[CREWMAN A]
There you go.
Every last file.
If there's a way to
defuse him, it's in there.
[RITSU]
No signs of falsification.
Relevant experimental
data's veracity confirmed.
I'll download a copy.
That should just about do it.
Now to get back and run
some tests of our own.
Yeah. We wouldn't want
to overstay our welcome.
Hey, pops!
[CREWMAN A]
Hm?
Heads up. Present for ya!
[yelps]
It's filled with
sweet-bean jelly,
so knock yourselves out.
[ALL]
Oh no.
Aw, don't sweat it.
Just tell the brass you
erred on the side of caution.
[NAGISA] We're very, very sorry
if we cause you any trouble!
At least you got to
kill some time, right?
[BOTH chuckle]
[MIZUI]
Look at 'em.
Swimming in zero gravity like
they're at a friend's place.
Stealing classified intel like
they're trading in video games.
Piercing the atmosphere like
they're just heading home
from a normal day at school.
Junior High sure isn't what it
used to be when I was a kid.
We just met the next
generation of heroes.
Come back soon.
Legally next time, though.
I'm an earthbound boy.
No offense, guys.
But rest assured,
the second I'm in power,
the space exploration program's
gettin' a big-time
budget increase.
[CREWMAN A]
Ha! I'll hold you to that.
Is it me, or does time
move faster in outer space?
[KARMA]
Mm.
[NAGISA] Let's hope
the odds are in our favor
for making it back
home in one piece.
Ritsu? Ritsu?
[RITSU]
Don't worry. I'm on it.
I've been crunching the
numbers like a boss.
Safety is virtually a
mathematical guarantee.
For all intents and purposes,
this ship is my physical body.
Sit back and relax.
I've got sensors scanning
all data parameters.
More than ever processed
before, in fact.
External temperature.
Air pressure.
Velocity. Even the scenery!
Pretty nifty, huh?
I also have a clear read
on your respiratory rate,
blood pressure, body
temperature, small talk.
To be so connected.
To be in motion.
It feels so...
...so wonderful!
This mission has been great.
We have the data we came for,
and my intelligence has evolved!
Hey. Do you wanna
know something?
It may be hard to believe,
but I've just processed
my very first emotion.
There's no other word for it.
Being a part of this class
has made me... happy.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Right on schedule!
I imagine it must've been
quite a grueling trip!
[yelps]
Are you all right, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI] It appears
I didn't need to intercede
in the negotiations after all.
I bet those daring cosmonauts
were enormously
impressed with you!
Probably, yeah.
[KORO-SENSEI] Hold tight, I'm
gonna give you a little shove!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Onward, to--! Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
[SUGINO] Yeah! They made it!
They're back home!
[YOSHIDA]
Woo-hoo!
[ISOGAI]
Keep going! Almost there!
[NAGISA]
We doubted each other.
Worried. Rattled sabers.
But when all was said and done,
at the end of that
crazy-long month,
we went into space!
[STUDENTS]
Hooray! They did it!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Phew.
What in the name
of God did you do?
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
I can't begin to conceive
how much damage.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh, this won't reflect on you.
I coerced the
students into going.
No one else knew of my plan.
You two have
plausible deniability,
At any rate, we have a
lovely bonus to show for it.
Human pilots yield much
better data than test dummies.
This will push the space program
forward by at least a decade!
Oh! And did I mention
Ritsu discovered
a more efficient trajectory
than previously known?
I give this to
you in good faith.
No hard feelings?
[KARASUMA growls]
You're unbelievable.
[STUDENTS cheering, laughing]
It's good to be home.
[MAEHARA]
Whoa! You gotta be kidding me!
I'm glad you got it and all,
but, I mean, for real.
This stuff might as
well be in Greek.
[OKUDA] Let me have a look.
I speak science, so...
Okay, in laymen's terms,
the things they were
doing on the Space Station
found that the risk of explosion
for a creature with tentacles
is inversely proportional
to its size.
Uh, that means the bigger
it is, the more stable.
The smallest ones
carry the greatest risk.
So a mouse would
be likely to explode,
whereas the probability
of a human with tentacles
going berserk and blowing up
is way lower than
originally thought.
Does that make sense?
Uh! So in other words--
Wait. Hang on, it says,
"The drug indicated below
is administered and
a silicon compound
used to stimulate
the flow of blood."
Oh, I get it.
By relieving muscular tension,
you decrease the chance of
the creature going critical.
Of course!
[ISOGAI, MAEHARA]
Tension?
[OKUDA] "When the following
conditions are satisfied,
the possibility of explosion,
even if initially high,
drops to less than one percent."
[ISOGAI]
One percent?
[OKUDA] "Likely, the organism's
cells will degenerate
before an explosion can occur,
evaporating over the course
of, on average, 90 years."
[TERASAKA] So this drug
they're talkin' about,
can we make it or what?
[OKUDA]
Yes, it's very simple.
As a matter of fact, the
compound I made a while ago
is almost identical
in structure.
[ALL]
Seriously?
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles nervously]
[FUWA]
Wow!
So, the key to solving this
has been front of us all along?
But are we sure?
I mean, it just seems a
little too easy is all.
[KAEDE]
Easy?
I don't think I'd call the
road we've been on an easy.
Kayano.
[KAEDE] My sister gave her
life to help Koro-sensei.
To keep him from going rogue.
And he chose to follow
in her footsteps,
risking his neck just to give
us a chance in the world.
If we hadn't put our
own lives on the line,
how far could we go?
Would we have found the drug?
Even more importantly, would
we have grown into a class
that could travel into space?
Look at it this way.
Less than one percent
is practically zero!
Even if we don't kill him,
we could still keep the
earth from blowing up!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Uh. Wait a minute. What
about the assassination?
[ALL]
Uh?
We've been working on it
as a class since first term.
Are we calling it off?
Is that what we've decided?
Uh... I guess this means
it kind of is, yeah.
Maybe...
[ISOGAI]
Should we talk it out more?
Nagisa, this was your idea.
What do you wanna do?
However minute the
possibility may be,
the government's not
going to cancel its plans.
Not as long a creature
like him is running loose.
I wanna be respectful
of the whole class,
particularly since
we've made it this far.
[NAGISA] We talked it
out and we decided.
If we couldn't kill Koro-sensei
by the March deadline,
we'd stop being
assassins-in-training
and opt for a more traditional
student-teacher dynamic.
But until then,
we'd brandish our blades
with the strength
of our convictions.
After all, in this classroom,
assassination isn't just the
bond we share with Koro-sensei,
it's the bond we
share with each other.
[NAGISA]
That was our decision.
Here we go.