[CLERK A] Oh!
Hey there, Big Teach!
Long time no see!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I know, right?
Thank goodness for payday!
[KORO-SENSEI] Your one-stop shop
for cheap, delicious junk food.
Well worth the trouble
of going incognito.
[WOMAN]
Hey, cut it out!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eh?
[MAN A]
Lighten up, doll face.
[WOMAN] Please,
I don't have time for this,
my students are expecting me.
So you're a teacher, are ya?
What would you say
to a li'l private tutoring
to help get our grades up?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Allow me to tutor you gentlemen
on how to flirt with a lady.
[MEN gasp, grunt]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Lesson One: First Impressions.
Know what your wheels
say about your game.
[MEN scream]
[MEN]
Why did you use pink?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
There is no Lesson Two.
Are you all right?
[WOMAN gasps]
Who says chivalry is dead?
You're a prince among men.
Thank you. I'll remember
this kindness always.
By the way...
I'm trying to find
Kunugigaoka Junior High.
Do you know where it is?
[KARASUMA] Okay.
Look alive, people.
Meet our newest addition
to the E Class faculty.
[IRINA] My name is
Ms. Irina Jelavic.
Nice to meet you all!
[SUGINO]
Talk about a knockout!
[OKAJIMA]
Knockers, more like.
[MEG] Does anybody
else think it's weird
--she's all over Koro-sensei?
--[IRINA] What are the chances?
--[NAKAMURA] Little bit, yeah.
--Who knew we'd be colleagues?
Oh, you're adorable!
We decided to bring on Ms.
Jelavic in the interest
of beefing up
the English curriculum.
No hard feelings, I hope.
She's, uh, very qualified.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No harm in that, is there?
She totally has a thing
for Koro-sensei.
I mean, she seems nice, so...
I guess it's kinda cute, right?
[NAGISA] Mm-hm. Might be
something we can use
to figure out
how to kill him, too.
--He seems thrown off
--[IRINA giggles]
by the attention
she's giving him.
Is it because she's human,
or because she's a woman?
His face changes color
to reflect his mood.
So what's the color for
hot and bothered?
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
[MAEHARA]
He is all about her.
[KAEDE]
Yeah. No mistaking that face.
[NAGISA]
Note: He blushes like a human.
Ahh... The more
I look at you,
the more I feel myself drawn in.
Those tiny, suppository eyes.
Those gelatinous joints.
I'm simply captivated
by the whole package!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, my. I, uh--
[OKANO] Don't fall for it,
she's trouble!
[NAKAMURA] No woman in her
right mind would be into you.
[NAGISA] He might be
a sucker for those looks.
But we know there's more going
on here than meets the eye.
If she's here, odds are
it's not just to
"beef up" our English studies.
[KORO-SENSEI] Let's see you
pass the ball! Come on!
And of course I had all
the usual close-range tricks
at the ready.
Apparently the art of
seduction works just as well
on whatever the hell he is.
[KARASUMA growls]
[KARASUMA] Irina Jelavic.
First-rate assassin.
Beautiful.
Intelligent. Athletic.
Fluent in a dozen languages.
No target is immune
to her charms,
whatever their nationality,
however well-guarded.
She wrote the book on
infiltration and approach.
As good as you are,
we can't just drop you
into this situation and expect
the usual tricks to work.
I know deep cover
is your specialty.
But this time you'll actually
have to actually teach.
Hah. As if I'll
be here long enough.
I'm a professional.
The octopus'll be pushing up
daisies before lunch.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heads up!
[KARMA]
Pass and kill!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nope. Pass.
[OKANO grunts]
Pass and kill! Huh?
--[KORO-SENSEI] Try again. Pass!
--[IRINA] Yoo-hoo!
Hope I'm not interrupting
anything, darling!
Mr. Karasuma tells me
you can go Mach 20
and I just had to see it
with my own eyes!
[KORO-SENSEI] Well, he might've
been exaggerating a tad.
I hate to ask this, but...
I would be ever so grateful
if you could fetch
some Vietnamese coffee.
I thought maybe you could
grab it while I run the students
through their English lesson.
[KORO-SENSEI]
But of course, mon cher!
It just so happens I know a
fabulous cafe in Vietnam.
[IRINA gasps]
[STUDENTS yell]
[school bell chimes]
Ah. It's about that
time, Ms. Irina.
I mean, that's the bell.
Shouldn't we head back?
Sure, whatever.
Knock yourselves out.
Teacher needs peace and quiet,
though, so make it a Study Hall.
[MAEHARA gasping]
And another thing.
Let's agree not to call me "Ms."
when the octopus isn't around.
And we're definitely not on a
first name basis. So drop it.
When he is around,
call me Ms. Jelavic.
Heh. So what's your
game, Ms. Jela-bitch?
No nicknames!
We got ourselves
a real pro here.
Just a word of
warning from those
who've been playin' the odds.
You're not gonna kill
the octopus without help.
Please, sweetheart.
You're a bunch of saplings.
Adults have their own way
of doing things, take note.
Speaking of which,
you're Nagisa Shiota, right?
[NAGISA gasps]
[NAGISA grunts]
[gasping, screaming]
[NAGISA grunting]
Do me a fav, show me
what you've got on him.
Grab your special
little notebook;
meet me in the faculty
lounge in ten minutes.
That goes for any of you
snot-nosed punks
who feel like you've got
intel worth sharing.
Give Ms. Jelavich
something useful.
and I'll let you go home
while these gentlemen
stand in for you.
This is what separates
the pros from the amateurs,
boys and girls:
connections and a little thing
we like to call "technique."
Now. Piss off. Go play.
Oh, and a word of warning from
those of us who know our job.
Get in the way, you die.
[NAGISA] That seductive,
femme fatale kiss.
Her, shady-looking companions.
The weight of her
off-handed threat.
Clearly we're not dealing with
a teacher, but a genuine pro.
Which, all things considered,
would be sort of cool
if she wasn't,
you know, such a bitch.
[IRINA] This assignment is the
first in which my objective
is to kill
an unidentified creature.
Everything should be
in order, though.
[NAGISA gasps]
[IRINA] The kid's intel has
given me a lot to work with.
[NAGISA whimpers]
A couple of us have actually
gotten as far as destroying
one of his tentacles,
but he just dodges
your next attack while
he lets it grow back.
I dunno. Maybe he
can only be killed
if all his tentacles
are destroyed at once?
Good luck hitting more
than one, though.
Also. If your plan
is to sneak up on him,
you probably don't
wanna smoke.
[IRINA]
Huh...?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hello there, children!
[NAGISA]
For a guy without a nose,
he's a bloodhound.
[IRINA]
This'll be a piece of cake.
My strategy is airtight.
I am the one and only Irina
Jelavic. The Closer.
The Go-to gal. I walk
between the raindrops,
--[MAEHARA] Uh...
--slip between--
--Ms. Jelabitch, ma'am?
--Arrgh!
Are you gonna teach us, or what?
[NAKAMURA] Yeah.
C'mon, Ms. Jelabitch.
[SUGAYA] No disrespect,
but you are a teacher,
aren't you,
Ms. Jelabitch?
[screams]
Ix-nay on the bitching!
The name is
JelaVIC, understand?
JelaBITCH is what I'll be if you
don't get the difference
through your thick,
prepubescent skulls!
Let's review!
My name is Jelavic.
"Jela-V!-vic!" Bite
your lower lip and hum!
[STUDENTS]
Vvv...
"V," excellent!
Now practice that sound
quietly for the next hour
while I ignore you.
[STUDENTS]
Lamest. Lesson. Ever.
[KARASUMA]
I understand you've brought in
a rather questionable trio.
Why wasn't I made aware
of this change of plan?
[IRINA] Ah! Don't judge
the books by their cover,
they're all consummate
professionals.
And so head-over-heels for me
they'll do whatever I ask.
Now, sit back
and enjoy the show.
It's almost go-time.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I've returned, mademoiselle!
With the Indian chai
you humbly requested.
[IRINA]
Ah! You're amazing!
My afternoon tea is going
to be absolutely fabulous!
One more favor, though.
Could we speak in private?
After fifth period? Like,
maybe out in the shed?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh dear.
Well, how could I
possibly say no?
I'll be there with certain-tea!
Get it? Certain-tea?
Because that's chai, you see.
[MIMURA]
Huh?
What? Oh, come on! You gotta
be kidding me! Seriously?
Wow. He's really falling for it.
I can't look. You'd think
he'd have more sense.
Mr. Karasuma, sir?
[KARASUMA]
Hm?
I get she's a pro, but she's not
exactly easy to get along with.
Yes, I know.
I'm sorry you kids
have to deal with her,
but the higher-ups seem
to think she's all that.
And, well, seeing what she's
been able to put together
in such a short time does
tend to make me agree with them.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So what is it you'd like to
speak in private about,
Ms. Irina, darling?
[IRINA]
Infiltration is an art.
One that requires
flexibility, finesse.
He's mine.
I just have to act quickly,
before he gets suspicious.
Oh, Koro-sensei,
I just can't stand it!
You'll think I'm a harlot,
but I simply can't
control myself around you!
[KORO-SENSEI squeals]
[IRINA] Your body, your
strength,
everything about you
drives me mad with longing!
[KORO-SENSEI] Ah,
well, yes-- I mean, ah--
[IRINA]
Does that make me a bad woman?
Am I bad?
That's right.
Keep those beady,
little eyes on me.
Don't pay attention
to your surroundings.
I spent all night
fixing this place up.
All for you, dirty boy.
All for you.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
[IRINA] This is what you want.
You can't fool me.
[KORO-SENSEI] I, uh, really
don't think we oughta
do this here!
[IRINA]
Goodbye, stupid.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
[IRINA]
It's been fun.
Don't be such a prude.
Let me get these clothes off.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What?!
Relax, darling, I'll be
au natural in a jiff.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Au natural...?
Whee-hee!
[IRINA]
Live ammo. Big guns.
M61. M134. M249.
Enough combined speed
and firepower
to take out a small army.
Who needs BB's when
you have the real thing?
I'm a pro.
I'll stick with actual weapons,
thank you very much.
And assignment complete in...
three, two, one, zero.
[IRINA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
A noble effort, madam,
but lead bullets have
no effect on me whatsoever.
In fact, once inside
my body, they melt.
[KORO-SENSEI] Look closely at my
face and tell me what you see.
[gasps] You...
You have four eyes?
[KORO-SENSEI] No. Two of
these holes are nostrils.
[IRINA] How am I
supposed to know that?!
[KORO-SENSEI] I noticed a
distinct metallic odor in here
since yesterday. Along with
the scent of adult man B.O.
The moment it hit me, I knew
something wasn't right.
[IRINA gasps]
For a guy without a nose,
he's a bloodhound.
[KORO-SENSEI] So you see,
I was simply pretending
to be ensnared by
your little ruse.
Fun, but all for nothing.
I've exposed you for
the uncreative hack you are.
[IRINA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] You could learn a
thing or two from my students.
Their assassination attempts
are much more imaginative.
Oh, and just out of curiosity.
Did the government dossier on me
mention that my preferred method
of retaliation... is grooming?
--[IRINA shrieks]
--[KORO-SENSEI cackles]
Uh, what was that?
I heard gunfire, a scream
and now slithering noise!
[IRINA]
No! [moans]
[IRINA moaning]
No...
[STUDENTS groan]
I really want to know what
he's doing to her in there.
Let's go!
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei!
[OKAJIMA]
Did you touch her boobs?!
[KORO-SENSEI sighs]
If only I had the time
to be really thorough.
But class isn't going to
teach itself, is it, children?
Um, what exactly
went on in there, sir?
[IRINA groans]
[NAGISA] Ms. Jelabitch
has been stuffed into
a tastefully retro gym outfit!
It would take longer for
me to describe the things he did
to this body than it
did for him to do them.
My back and shoulders
have never felt looser.
He somehow worked in
a lymphatic oil massage.
A change of clothes,
just because.
And he still had time to do
this thing with his tentacles.
[MIMURA, OKAJIMA]
What thing with his tentacles?!
Koro-sensei, what is
she talking about?
[KORO-SENSEI] Uh. Adults
sometimes need special care.
[NAGISA]
I don't trust that look.
[KORO-SENSEI] Come now. Back to
the classroom, boys and girls.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir.
[IRINA]
Unbelievable.
I've never been
so humiliated in all my life!
I am a professional, damn it!
The octopus will pay!
[STUDENTS groan]
[IRINA]
If he thinks I'm out of ideas,
that yellow, wiggly monstrosity
has another thing coming!
I just need fresh supplies!
Oh, come on! What's with
the Wi-Fi in this place?!
Are we on Mars?!
Wow. Looks like
Ms. Jelabitch is pissed off.
I know my pride
would be in shambles
if my plan had gone tits up.
[snarls]
Excuse me, Miss?
Ugh. What?
If you're not actually
going to teach us anything,
you mind if we swap
you out for Koro-sensei?
It's just, we've got entrance
exams coming up, and--
[IRINA] Hah!
You wanna swap me out
for that disgusting creature?!
You're worried about
entrance exams
when the planet is on notice?!
Must be paradise not knowing
your ass from
a hole in the ground.
Give it a rest.
Even if the Earth wasn't on
the brink of destruction,
entrance exams are for
students with a future.
[STUDENTS growl]
[IRINA] News flash:
that's not any of you losers.
How 'bout this, kids?
Forget the "studying."
Help me brainstorm on how to
kill the octopus
and I'll give you a nice
percentage of the reward money.
That's the best deal any
of you E Class jerkoffs
are gonna get out of life.
Otherwise, knock it off
with the whining and let--
[MAEHARA]
Get out.
[IRINA]
Ah?
--[STUDENTS growl]
--[IRINA whimpers]
[MAEHARA] Now, you're
just a plain ol' bitch!
[TOKA]
We want Koro-sensei back!
That's it! I will make you
rue the day you were born!
Yeah! Go ahead,
we dare you, bitch!
Your boobs are way
too big to be a teacher!
[NAGISA]
Seriously?!
[KARASUMA growls]
[IRINA] Someone oughta
slap the piss out of them!
I am too fine a woman to be
one-upped by a bunch of punks!
They'd be lucky to lick
the mud off my stilettos!
In case you haven't
noticed, sweetheart,
the children don't exactly
agree with that assessment.
If you're gonna stick around
for another attempt,
I suggest you suck it up,
march in there
and give them an apology.
Do what?!
I am an accomplished assassin,
not a glorified
rugrat wrangler!
Let me focus on
what I'm qualified for!
[sighs] Oh, fine. Whatever.
Just come with me, please.
[KORO-SENSEI] Erromango.
One of the islands of Vanuatu,
otherwise known as
the New Hebrides.
Okay. So exactly what
the hell is he doing?
Poring over and
writing out test questions.
He's done this every
Wednesday during sixth period
since I've been here.
Quick as the bastard is,
you wouldn't think
it'd take him so long.
I mean, at Mach 20, I'd
imagine the tests would be
written out and
ready to go by now.
[KARASUMA] They're tailored
to each individual student.
[gasps]
[KARASUMA] He takes into account
which subjects they're good at,
where they need improvement,
and hands out a test
designed specifically for them.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No denying that Chiba
has spatial relations down pat.
Let's give him a problem
that'll really kick-start
his lateral thinking.
His IQ is off
the charts, literally.
His speed puts every weapon
we have to shame.
He's dangerous, contradictory,
and a damn-near perfect teacher.
[TOKA]
Ha-ha!
[RYUNOSUKE grunts]
Look at the kids.
Tell me what you see.
[IRINA] Huh? They're just
screwing around.
They're fine-tuning
the necessary
hand-eye coordination skills
to hit a moving target.
I call it,
--Assassination Badminton,
--[SUGINO] Take that!
--[IRINA] What?
--[KIMURA] Good thrust!
Three points!
Everyone has two roles here.
Assassin and student.
Teacher and target.
It's a bizarre classroom this
creature's created,
not a place for easy answers
or tidy resolutions.
Or one where we can
afford to fit ourselves
into simple categories.
I understand wanting to take
pride in yourself
as a professional,
but if you can't cut it
as both assassin and
teacher, you're toast.
[IRINA gasps]
[MAEHARA]
Nice return.
[TOKA]
Yeah. Whatever.
You wanna stay here,
keep at it, fine. Be my guest.
Just treat those kids
with respect.
[IRINA sighs]
What word does
"incredible" modify?
You know this one.
Read it aloud.
[STUDENTS]
"Y-You are incredible in bed."
[IRINA] I was once
took out an American VIP.
Literally. I had my
feminine grace to thank
for getting me close
to the target.
The poor dupe fell for me
hook, line, and sinker.
"You are incredible in bed,"
he told me.
Incredible, in this case,
modifies the word you.
[NAGISA] That's the example
you use with Junior High kids?!
To learn grammar, you've
got to see how it works
in the real world.
Like a full immersion course
in a foreign language.
Take a lover that speaks it
and you can't miss.
I know grammar seems
boring and technical,
but it's what underpins
how we communicate.
Communication is key in
my line of work, and in life.
Whether speaking English,
French, Portuguese,
what have you, all people
have an underlying need
to express their feelings.
That's why this is important.
The examples may be risqué,
but they come from
real-life scenarios. They will
all have either been said by me,
or to me by someone else.
One day, you might use
or hear them yourselves.
[NAKAMURA, OKAJIMA]
Communication.
Don't expect me
to be like the octopus.
He can help you with
your entrance exams.
Which isn't without
value, I suppose.
All I can do is help you learn
the art of conversation.
Here's the deal: If after a
while, you think this is stupid,
that I'm not a teacher, fine.
I'll give up
my assignment and leave.
So, this oughta put us
on the level, right?
Oh, and... I'm sorry about
being... such a bitch.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[STUDENTS laughing]
Wow. Talk about a one-eighty.
First, you wanna kill us,
now you're acting like a wuss.
[IRINA gasps]
I gotta say, you make a
more convincing teacher
with this attitude.
Guess this means we shouldn't
call you Ms. Jelabitch anymore.
[gasps]
You're giving me a chance?
You're not upset with me?
[MEG] To be totally fair, we
didn't exactly get off
on the right foot
with that nickname.
[OKANO]
Maybe not.
But we've got to
call her something.
[MAEHARA]
How 'bout "Ms. Hellabitch"?
[IRINA grunts]
Uh... Or... We could
just agree to move away
from the whole bitch
motif altogether.
I'm not opposed to going by
Irina if you guys don't mind
--calling a teacher by--
--Yeah, I'm sorry.
I wouldn't plan on the bitch
thing going away any time soon.
[IRINA gasps]
[OKANO] Mm-hm! Not that
Ms. Irina isn't a pretty name,
it's just not as fun
to say as Hellabitch.
[HINANO]
Professor Bitch sounds classy.
How 'bout we do that?
[OKAJIMA]
I vote for that one.
Professor Bitch all the way.
[IRINA shrieks]
I hate you little turds so much!
[STUDENTS laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI] She seems
to be settling in nicely.
[KARASUMA]
Eh. More or less.
[IRINA] Do you know
who you're messing with?!
I will end you!
[KORO-SENSEI] Thank you
for bringing a new teacher,
Mr. Karasuma. She's a bit
rough around the edges,
perhaps, but a welcome
addition to our little family,
I think. Who better to spruce
up the language arts syllabus
than a globe-trotting
assassin-slash-temptress
like her?
[KARASUMA]
Impossible.
There's no way you've
coulda seen this coming.
[KORO-SENSEI]
If you'll excuse me...
[KARASUMA]
Whenever he's pressed to say why
he started teaching E Class,
he dodges the question.
But whatever his reasons, he's
not only turned it into
the perfect training
ground for assassins.
It may just be the perfect
training ground for life.
[HINANO] You're so
adorable when you're mad.
[IRINA]
No, I am not!
[KARASUMA] Bastard's got us all
wrapped around his tentacles.
He knows what he's doing.
No doubt about it.