[NAGISA]
Stop it, Kayano!
This is insane!
If you think I care...
...you're wrong.
[KAEDE] When my mind's fixed on
something, I just keep rolling!
[NAGISA] This is the real
Kayano, not the character.
She's been in boss-battle mode
for maybe 15 seconds
and already the tentacles have
gotten a foothold on her brain.
If she's that far gone,
it's too late.
Whether she gets her revenge
on Koro-sensei or not,
another few minutes of this...
...she's dead.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Kayano...
Kill you! Murderer!
Kill you! Kill you!
[KAEDE]
Koro-sensei...
Please...
Save me...
[KAEDE]
Die! Die! Die! Die!
You hear me?!
You're going to die!
But if he does,
he won't be the only one...
We have to do something, guys.
What, we just stand
here while her life's
being eaten away like this?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Children!
Koro-sensei?!
Just a face now?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sorry. Partial clone.
I'm afraid Kayano's attacks
aren't leaving me
a lot of wiggle room.
Believe me, it's all I can do to
project an afterimage of this.
[SUGAYA]
It's kinda cool, actually.
[KORO-SENSEI] Her tentacles
must be removed ASAP!
They're putting out this
infernal heat at tremendous cost
to her body!
She's so bent on killing me,
she's lost all reason!
If we don't act quickly,
they'll sap her life force
and kill the poor girl!
Trouble is, so long as
her bloodlust equals
that of the tentacles,
they'll be rooted into
her nervous system,
impossible to extract!
Talking her down isn't
an option as it was with Itona.
We simply don't have the time!
So... what do we do?
[KORO-SENSEI]
The only thing we can.
I'll have to pull 'em
out as we fight.
I'll have to let her hit
my most vulnerable spot--
the area beneath my tie.
My heart.
Should she completely
destroy it, death is certain.
But if she feels as though
she's done me in,
her tentacles will be
satisfied, for a moment.
One of you must exploit that
tiny window of opportunity
to make Kayano forget
her bloodlust.
[KIRARA]
Forget it? How?
[KORO-SENSEI]
By any means necessary.
Whatever it takes to get
her mind off assassination!
Alas, it's the only
thing I can't do.
If her intended target were
to try anything funny,
her bloodlust would
only intensify.
Quell it, however,
and the tentacles' bond
will temporarily break.
Their grip on Kayano's nervous
system will be loosened
just enough to make extraction
possible without major damage.
Yeah, but she'd--
I mean, the tentacles
would be on your heart
the whole time, right?
Wouldn't you die before we
could get them off of her?
[KORO-SENSEI] I might be able
to postpone the moment of death
long enough to regenerate,
but optimistically
the odds are 50-50.
--Then no!
--[KORO-SENSEI] Don't despair!
The possibility of E Class
not being allowed to graduate
is far worse than
the prospect of my demise.
[yells]
But... Ugh! Really?
He wants them to jump
into the fray?
These kids aren't magicians!
What does he expect them
to do against that?
Mimura!
Give us some air guitar.
--What?
--Come on, man!
Show her your mad skills!
But she's gonna go after me!
[YOSHIDA]
Just do it!
[NAKAMURA]
That's ridiculous!
[NAGISA]
The clap stunner?
No. Her mental frequency's
too out of whack.
I'd never find an opening.
At best, she'd just ignore me.
Knives? Guns?
Out of the question.
We don't want to hurt her.
There has to be something.
What've we all been doing
with ourselves the past year?
We're supposed to be
trained assassins,
experts in this kind of stuff!
[gasps]
[NAGISA] Hold on,
there's that one killer move.
[KAEDE screams]
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[KAEDE]
Die! Die! Die!
Die!
[screams]
[coughs]
[KAEDE]
Gotcha!
[screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I made a promise to your sister.
Forgive me. I'm not
letting you out of my grasp.
[gasps]
Nagisa...
What're you doing?
[screaming]
[gasping]
[hums]
[NAGISA]
I won't let you say it, Kayano.
That this was all an act.
[KAEDE gasps]
[NAGISA]
We've made too many memories.
Been through too much together.
[KAEDE whimpers]
[NAGISA] I won't let you say the
only thing you cared about...
...was revenge.
[KAEDE whimpers]
Will this do? Please say yes.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well done, Nagisa!
They'll come out with ease!
[inaudible]
[OKUDA]
Is she...
Is she all right?
Is this over now?
[KORO-SENSEI]
I think so. Probably.
The important thing is that
she get plenty of rest.
[sighs]
Whew, now that was a kiss!
Look at you, goin' all
Prince Charming!
Way to go, Nagisa!
Don't make it a thing.
I was distracting her from
her bloodlust, that's all.
I'll apologize to her
when she wakes up, so...
[IRINA] Fifteen hits
on a ten second kiss
is noting to write
home about honey.
I'm disappointed...
"Fifteen hits"?
If you're gonna kiss, get in
there like there's no tomorrow.
Go big or go home.
You could've pulled off
a minimum of 40 hits.
Huh--my upper limit's
around 25...
Why do you guys make me
want to hate this place?
It's a red letter day
if I get to 20.
[KORO-SENSEI retches]
[STUDENTS]
Koro-sensei!
[KORO-SENSEI pants]
I'm fine...
It'll just take a little while
for my heart to fully recover.
I realize you're waiting for an
explanation, but please...
Indulge me with your
patience a bit longer.
[gunshot]
[gasping]
[SHIRO]
Stop playing the deathbed angle.
You've clearly recouped
enough to dodge.
It's Shiro.
[SHIRO]
Pathetic little twit.
For someone so willing to
sacrifice themselves
for the sake of retribution.
You'd think she'd have managed
something a little more
on the nose than this.
Quite the monster, aren't you?
How many would-be assassins have
you sent away empty-handed
in the past year?
Well... There are still at least
two you haven't deflected.
[SHIRO]
And I will be the last.
Yes, the one from whom
you stole everything.
To whom, in the end,
you will give your life.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah. So it is you.
I thought I recognized
that twisted genius.
This, boys and girls,
is Yanagisawa.
Come, 2.0.
[SHIRO]
March is upon us
and with it, a perfect end
to an accursed life.
[FUWA]
What's with that guy?
[KAEDE groans]
What happened?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah, Kayano. Thank goodness.
Are you, uh... You okay?
[KAEDE]
Mm-hmm...
So you're back?
At first, I was
driven by bloodlust.
But, the more time
I spent with Koro-sensei,
the less and less
it seemed to matter.
I started to think,
"What's his story?
What about him don't I know?
Should I hold off killing him
till I get the whole picture?"
But about that time,
the tentacles took control.
They refused to let me wait.
I'm so stupid...
Assassination's been about
self-discovery for you,
while I've spent the past year
secretly obsessed with revenge.
[NAGISA]
Kayano.
It's 'cause of you I quit
feeling self-conscious
about my hair.
The first time we met,
you pretty much called it out
and look at me now, right?
And like you said,
Koro-sensei's name...
You're the one who
gave it to him, remember?
Maybe you were just
playing a role. Okay, fine.
Doesn't mean it wasn't
a part of you
or that our friendship
was based on a lie.
We all wear masks
from time to time.
We're all different on the
inside than on the out.
It's still the real you.
[NAGISA]
Here's the deal:
Koro-sensei owes us
an explanation as a class.
None of us expects him
to be a saint.
We know he doesn't
always do the right thing.
But as a class,
let's hear his story.
[KAEDE]
Okay...
And thanks...
It's nice to finally be real...
Don't worry, sir.
What's done is done.
As long as you tell us
the truth, we'll accept it.
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Thank you.
I'd hoped to never revisit
this chapter of my life.
And yet... I have little choice.
Your trust is vital to me--
I would never do
anything to break it.
Never jeopardize our bond.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Last summer, on the island,
Mr. Karasuma said of
Miss Irina, if you'll recall:
"There's a lot more to a good
assassin than meets the eye."
Those words are
especially relevant here.
You see, children,
this class represents
my first go as a teacher.
But, all things considered,
I think it's fair to assert
I've more than risen
to the challenge.
[KORO-SENSEI] After all,
I am a gifted improviser.
[gasps]
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Then... you mean...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes.
Until two years ago, I was the
assassin known as the Reaper.
[gasping]
[KORO-SENSEI]
And that's not all.
Whether you kill me or not,
come March, I'm doomed.
Either I go alone--or I take
the Earth with me.
That's the only aspect of your
future assassinating me
can change.
[NAGISA gasps]
[NAGISA]
We wanted his story.
He delivered.
These were his memories
of being human.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Born in darkness,
he grew to disdain the light.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Weaned on soul-crushing poverty,
a child of the slums, he knew
only ugliness and degradation.
Life taught him that he could
only rely on three things:
Skill, money, and death.
Naturally, the assassin's
path beckoned.
Those stronger than himself,
he killed with knowledge.
Those more knowing,
he killed with strength.
Those gifted with both,
he killed with surpassing charm.
When the number of his
victims reached a thousand,
fittingly, rumor
christened him the Reaper.
[SHIRO]
Watch how you handle this one.
Assume he can kill you
regardless of setting
or apparent disadvantage.
Of course, it's hard to
imagine a more disadvantageous
setting for him than this.
They don't come more
clear-headed or hard-boiled.
There's no next-of-kin
to complain if he dies.
The perfect guinea pig
for our experiment
if ever there was one.
How lucky we are
to have found him.
[SHIRO]
Listen closely, guinea pig.
You may have been
the Reaper out there,
in here, you're a specimen.
Your daily routine is going
to be very unpleasant.
[door opens]
[AGURI]
Wow! That's a shock!
You don't look like
a ruthless killer.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Someone drew the short straw.
Look, ma'am.
I won't do anything.
Can't you just get me
out of here please?
Sorry. It's just
that I've developed
an intense allergy
to being murdered.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I like her. She can be useful.
[KORO-SENSEI] There's only
one thing that bothers me.
What's with the shirt?!
I'm Aguri Yukimura.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
[SHIRO]
ATPase. Rebalance phase.
Give him 40 units
of SOD inhibitor.
[MALE RESEARCHER]
Yes, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
They're wide open.
But killing them now
would be... premature.
[SHIRO]
Hmm?
--[door opens]
--Ah!
Excellent work today.
Take a little while to relax.
I'll check your vitals in a few.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nice shirt.
It's even dorkier
than the last one.
[AGURI]
Huh?! Oh, come on!
I'm just trying to add
a little color to your life!
I thought you'd appreciate it!
To be honest,
it grinds my gears.
Wish I'd known that before
I fell in love with this brand.
Ugh. I guess my students
aren't the only ones
who think it's lame.
Students?
[SHIRO]
Aguri!
Is there any reason a simple
data check takes so long?!
[AGURI] I-I'm sorry,
Kotaro, we were just--
[grunts]
[AGURI groans]
If your dolt of a father weren't
one of my core subcontractors,
it'd be you on the other
side of the glass!
You owe me!
I let you slide on
the connubial duties,
but here, I expect
professionalism!
[SHIRO]
See you tomorrow, guinea pig.
It's going to be a busy day.
[SHIRO chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI grunts, groans]
[KORO-SENSEI] The chief ambition
of Yanagisawa's research
was to generate
organic antimatter.
To that end, he would
stop at nothing.
He spliced the particle
acceleration cycle
necessary for antimatter into
the life cycle of a cell,
effectively priming the cell's
engine and infusing it
with astonishing power.
Hey, Yanagisawa?
There's no feeling
in my hands or feet.
And I'm chilled to the bone.
"Mister" Yanagisawa!
Ugh. And peripheral neuropathy
is par for the course.
[MALE RESEARCHER] I recommend we
take him off the alkaloid, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI] If I can subtly
manipulate the process myself,
I'll boost the
likelihood of success.
[KORO-SENSEI] Destructive powers
beyond all measure will be mine.
Wow! Lots to get to
on the checklist today!
Best get started if I don't
wanna get smacked around.
I take it that's a
frequent worry for you.
[AGURI]
Oh, yeah.
Can't let the sense
get knocked out of me.
There'd be nothing
to pass on to my class.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Your class?
[SHIRO]
Aguri! Damn it, woman!
Why must you try my patience?!
I-I was just getting
started, dear!
[SHIRO] Put those
clerical skills to use!
Or have I overestimated your
capacity for basic grunt work?
You have one job!
Learn to do it!
Huh?
What did you do?
Mister Reaper, you--
He's just immobilized, ma'am.
Relax. You have a classroom
to think about, right?
[chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] After three
months in that dreadful place,
the teacher and the killer
were as open with each other
as old friends.
[AGURI sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Quadratic equations?
Might I suggest you
dress them up a little?
Never go too easy
on college prep school students.
[AGURI]
Huh?
The mercenary giving career
advice to the educator?
You know, I'm starting to think
you're better suited
to my teaching gig than me.
Ah, well, I could
definitely play the part
if the job called for it.
But, uh... I'm not
cut out for the real thing.
Huh...?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Believe it or not,
I had a protégé once.
He betrayed me.
How do you think I
wound up in this place?
[REAPER]
Uh-oh.
It looks as though you'll
be passing on more
than just your skill set.
Don't worry, though.
Your name will live in infamy
through a thousand faces.
Goodbye, sir. It's been fun.
A shame you
never really knew me.
Maybe another time.
[KORO-SENSEI]
How could I be so blind?
I cultivated his abilities.
Gauged his progress
in minute detail.
[AGURI]
He wanted to be seen.
Huh?
[AGURI]
He wanted your approval.
Everything he did was just
to get your attention.
Believe me.
But I watched the boy
like a hawk.
Everyone wants attention.
That's the key
to winning them over.
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[SHIRO]
Break time's over, guinea pig.
Back to work.
On the table, please.
We have some tests to run.
[MALE RESEARCHER]
The changes our subject's body
is undergoing are unprecedented.
I hate to think of
the havoc he'll cause
when he decides he's had enough.
Oh, if he tries to escape,
taking Aguri hostage will be
the linchpin of his strategy.
Come now. You didn't
suppose I gave her this job
out of the goodness
of my heart?
She's a pawn. A sacrificial
lamb to gauge his mileage.
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[retching]
[AGURI gasps]
[MALE RESEARCHER] This is
the reaction we anticipated.
It's all right. He'll be fine.
[KORO-SENSEI coughs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
She was part of the experiment.
The Reaper was turning into
something altogether inhuman.
She suspected as much.
But didn't wish to burden
her superiors with questions.
[AGURI]
Great job again today.
Take a second
to catch your breath
and I'll take your vitals.
[AGURI] I'll stick around so
we can visit for a while.
[KORO-SENSEI] She looked
straight ahead and smiled.
Sweet and lighthearted as ever.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of course...
Everyone wants
attention, approval.
Sounds lovely.
You bring the exam questions?
[KORO-SENSEI]
The legendary killer
who'd never shown
himself to anyone,
at last understood
the joy of being seen.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The seasons changed.
A new school year began.
A fresh batch of students
gathered under the roof
of Kunugigaoka's Class 3-E.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Little did they know,
in only two week's time,
the moon would become
a permanent crescent.