[HINANO] What cha think,
Professor Bitch?
Is the gear we got
yesterday awesome or what?
[OKANO]
Right?
Mr. K sure knows how to
kick things up a notch!
[IRINA chuckles]
FYI, I had a teeny bit of
input in the overall design.
For which, you're welcome.
That oaf wanted the same
style for the whole class.
[OKANO]
Glad he vetoed the "Irina."
[TOKA] It's cute,
just not super functional.
Yeah, well.
'Least one of your teachers
understands women.
Blockhead couldn't even be
bothered to get me a present.
[ALL]
Huh?
[TOKA gasps]
Oh, no! Of course! October
tenth was four days ago!
[OKANO, HINANO]
Huh? Professor Bitch's birthday!
[IRINA]
Before I came here,
I had legions of sugar daddies
falling all over themselves
to buy me expensive things.
Now?
If it doesn't come from
him, I'm not interested.
What the hell is wrong with me?
And why haven't I been able
to get ahold of Lovro?
Being alone sucks.
Professor Bitch, do you
have a little time to go over
some more
conversational francais?
[IRINA]
Do what?
Oh, that's right.
You had your heart set
on working overseas.
Yeah. Oh, excuse me,
I meant to say oui.
Well, all right then, take
a seat and we'll drill--
[MEG]
Actually, the weather's so nice,
I was thinking we
could do this outside.
[IRINA]
But why?
[MEG]
C'mon! It'll be fun!
[OKAJIMA] Man, those two
are lucky to have us around
to push things along.
We're a go.
The Fox and the Hound
have been separated.
We'll keep our fingers crossed
for the Birthday Present Squad.
Right, let's do this.
Now what exactly are you
supposed to get someone
who already has
two of everything?
[KAEDE]
It's not gonna be easy.
Everybody pitched in.
Not a whole lot, but
it's better than nothing.
Question is, will it be enough
to by a proper grown-up gift?
[FLORIST]
Hey, over here!
Everything thing end up
okay with that man?
You know, the old-timer
on the bicycle?
[NAGISA]
Uh...
You're the flower guy who
called the ambulance!
He managed to forgive us after
a couple of weeks, yeah.
Uh, thanks for helping us out.
No sweat. I'm glad it
wasn't as bad as it looked.
Beg pardon, I couldn't
help but overhear
you're in the market
for a grown-up gift?
Yes! Yes we are!
[FLORIST] Well, what about
something like this?
Oh, I get it! A bouquet!
[FLORIST] In this day and age,
we can have whatever we want.
But flowers are still
the go-to gift of choice.
Why do you suppose that is?
[STUDENTS]
Hm?
[FLORIST]
It's not just about romance.
Their color, their
shape, and scent.
The fact that they don't last.
Flowers are an ideal metaphor
for the human condition.
Oh my. You're a
persuasive salesman, sir.
Quite the, poetic little speech.
That calculator part
of the symbolism?
Hey, I'm just trying
to make a living.
So, uh, you in?
I'll cut you a deal.
It's flowery fate.
[TOKA]
Wow! Then what?
Is there some magic word that
brings a Frenchman to his knees?
What's with you today, Toka?
You've never been so enthralled;
you're hanging on every word.
Well, yeah,
I wanna learn French.
Hey, Miss?
Can you play piano for us
like you did at the hotel?
C'mon, Professor Bitch!
Let me draw you in one
of your killer poses!
Hold on! I asked
her first, y'know!
[IRINA]
Uhh...
[IRINA] What's the deal with
these brats all of a sudden?
I'm so popular!
Ha! Don't fret my
little darlings!
There's enough Professor
Bitch to go around!
Just don't get turned on.
That would be crossing the line.
It's a very nice bouquet of
flowers, don't get me wrong.
[KARASUMA]
But why me?
They'd mean so much
more coming from you.
[NAGISA] Ugh. Can somebody
actually be this clueless?
Mr. K, please.
Look at it this way:
Professor Bitch is a vital
asset to the mission.
All in a day's work, sir.
Winning over your colleague
can only help things, right?
Hah. Just let her think
they're from you. Cool?
I see your point.
Very well. I'll do it.
Thanks for your dedication.
--[IRINA chuckling]
--[phone buzzing]
[STUDENTS murmuring]
Wait, I...
Come on, you don't all have
to leave at the same time.
Well damn. How do you like that?
Urgh. Nice. Absolutely perfect.
I'm right back to being
Miss Lonely Hearts.
Hey, Karasuma! You won't
believe what just happened!
Those self-centered brats--
Oh, Irina. Good timing.
[IRINA]
Uh... What is this?
I know I'm late,
but... Happy Birthday.
Wait, these're for me?
And they're from you?
[KARASUMA] Sorry I let
the actual day slip by.
Things got busy.
[IRINA]
No, it's fine. I'm delighted.
Thank you so much.
You old dog!
I thought you forgot it!
Is this real, or is there
something up your sleeve?
I do want to mark the occasion.
This is the first and
last of your birthdays
we'll celebrate together.
Oh, don't be silly. What
is that supposed to mean?
Just what it sounds like.
Stands to reason, yes?
Either the mission's going
to end or the world will.
One way or the other, in half
a year, this'll be over.
[KARASUMA]
Hm?
Oh. Hey there.
Well, we're screwed.
[IRINA] I figured you
had to be behind this.
A bouquet of flowers, huh?
Like the square would think of
doing something like that for me
of his own will.
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[IRINA]
You enjoy yourselves?
Stringing me along so you
can watch a pro assassin
get her pathetic
little hopes up.
[KORO-SENSEI] That's not
the case at all, Miss Irina!
The children's intentions
were utterly pure--
[IRINA]
Save it, Octorazzi!
Who gives a damn?
This is a business
relationship, nothing more.
I've been so caught
up in my role,
I've forgotten who I really am.
[IRINA]
You've opened my eyes.
Best birthday present
ever. Thank you.
[SUGINO]
Hold on!
Professor Bitch, please!
[MAEHARA] Not to point
fingers or anything, Mr. K,
but that was kind of cold
of you, don't you think?
[OKANO] Don't tell us you still
haven't noticed how she feels?
You kids don't really believe
I'm that oblivious, do you?
I'm a heartless bastard
for good reason.
Emotions can't be allowed
to get in the way
of what needs to be done.
We're professionals.
If her feelings for me
can dull her blade,
then she's not qualified
to be an assassin.
That's all there is to it.
But, Mr. Karasuma...
[IRINA yells]
I am so pissed off right now!
Karasu-- To hell with
that! More like Crapsuma!
Damn! It's hard to say!
[IRINA] Maybe...
Maybe it's time to leave.
What's left for me here anyway?
Nothing. Not with
what I'm capable of.
[NAGISA] After that, Professor
Bitch essentially disappeared.
She hasn't been
here in three days.
We really crossed the
line this time, guys.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well, I'm off.
You can call me if there's
any news on Miss Irina.
Meanwhile, there's a fútbol
tournament in Brazil
I must attend.
So... ciao!
Okay then, guess
he's outta here.
What's the deal with him
and soccer all of a sudden?
[MAEHARA] Typical
"once-every-four-years" fan.
What happened to baseball?
I'm starting to get worried.
I just hope she's okay.
Yeah, no. Not much
luck getting through.
My GPS scan is
coming up negative.
No matches on the
closed-circuit feeds either.
Seriously.
You don't think she would leave
over something like this?
[FLORIST]
I'm sure that can't be the case.
After all, there's still
something important
you need her to do.
Yes, exactly. Plus she knows
we like having her around.
[FLORIST]
Right.
You children have bonded
rather nicely with her,
there's no denying that.
You see,
my preliminary reconnaissance
confirmed as much.
Your connection gives me
something very handy to exploit.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[ALL gasping]
[NAGISA]
It was so... so casual.
He walked in like
he owned the place.
[FLORIST]
Hello.
I'm the assassin commonly
known as The Reaper.
And today, boys and girls,
class it going to be fun.
[KIMURA]
What the--?
[RYUNOSUKE]
It's him.
A flower tends to throw
people off guard.
There's hardly a soul alive
immune to their charm.
Remember my sales pitch?
Nagisa, you were taken in.
[REAPER] But you see, there's
a reason flowers evolved
into such lovely,
fragrant varieties.
Ritsu, would you bring
up the image I sent?
[gasps]
[REAPER] Their purpose
is to draw insects.
Is that Professor Bitch?
[REAPER]
I'll cut to the chase.
It's simple. If you
want her to live,
show up when and
where I tell you to.
And yes, I mean
the entire class.
Not a word of this
to your teachers.
'Course, I can understand
if you're not comfortable
with those terms.
If you'd rather not come,
there's always the option
of sending her to you.
In tiny, individual wrapped
pieces. One per student.
If that's the preference, fine.
Though, one of you will
likely be my next flower.
[KARMA]
We didn't see him coming.
That's when it dawned on me.
What scared me most of
all was not being afraid.
'Kay, first off,
we got no obligation to
save that pushy bitch,
so thanks for playin',
but no dice.
Second, what's to stop us from
beatin' the piss out of you
right here and now,
ya kidnappin' bastard?
A bold assessment,
but entirely wrong.
The woman means more
to you than you know.
In fact, I suspect that
if you were to let her die,
you'd be beside yourselves.
As to your second point,
no human being is capable
of taking down the Reaper.
[REAPER]
Conversely,
human beings are the
Reaper's preferred prey.
"Come to the location
shown on the map.
Arrive as a group at
six P.M. and tell no one."
Huh.
Exactly like with
Takaoka and Shiro.
They wanna take us hostage.
Draw out Koro-sensei
with us as the bait.
Damn!
[TERASAKA]
We usin' these?
We're doing this to
protect someone. So, yes.
I don't care if he's
the greatest assassin
who's ever lived,
we're not about to let
that oily SOB's plan
go off without a hitch.
[MAEHARA]
That's gotta be the way in.
Bird's eye
loop-around's negative.
There's no sign of
anybody close by.
Makes it more ominous.
'Kay, Ritsu.
If we don't all make it
back here by midnight,
tell Koro-sensei
what's going on.
Got it. Good luck.
Be stay safe, everyone.
[ISOGAI]
Let's go!
[MAEHARA]
Lotta space he's got.
[crackling]
[REAPER] Is that all of you?
Good. Watch the doors.
Ah. You like to keep an eye
on us, huh? Kinda kinky.
Reaper, Peeper. All right.
Sure, why not?
Look, we've held up
our end of the bargain!
So give back Professor Bitch,
and let us get on
with our lives, okay?
[ALL gasp]
What the hell?
Whoa! The whole
room's going down!
Trap is complete.
Ensnaring you as a group
is the best way.
Saves me a lot of time.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENTS]
Professor Bitch!
Ugh! Crap!
[REAPER]
No worries.
If he comes quietly,
no one gets killed.
[OKAJIMA] What about if we,
like, resist or something?
Would you be mad
enough to kill us then?
Oh, relax. It's pitiful
how scared you are.
Uh, sorry, I can't
really do much about it.
Here! This section
sounds hollow!
[TAKEBAYASHI]
A fitted charge.
[OKUDA]
A few smokescreen capsules.
[bang]
[gasps]
[REAPER chuckles]
Yes, good! Make it fun!
[ISOGAI]
Okay. Moment of truth's upon us.
[static]
[REAPER]
Hello, E-Class? Can you hear me?
Nice work. Honestly,
I'm happy you escaped.
It'll be a good warm-up
for the real game.
I expect great things.
I knew it. It's a game to him.
[NAGISA]
This isn't some vindictive act,
like with Takaoka.
It's different.
He's an unknown quantity.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Seven to one.
[BRAZILIANS]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mmm-hmmm. Indeed.
Letting XY stand
for seven to one
gives us a lovely
math problem...
[BRAZILIANS yelling]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, dear me,
I seem to have angered
the locals somehow.
Did I insult a sacred custom?
I ought to pick Maehara's brain
on this. He knows soccer.
[OPERATOR] We're sorry,
the number you've dialed
is out of range.
[KORO-SENSEI] Uh. Isogai, then?
Perhaps Hinata. Or Terasaka.
I have a bad feeling about this.
We'll intercept him here.
Whichever way he
decides to come from,
we'll still have him
outnumbered, so stay alert.
Ritsu, we need
some backup, 'kay?
Yeah, not feelin' it.
Be realistic, like I'm gonna
go up against the Reaper.
[RITSU] I'd rather power
down than, like, do stuff.
[STUDENTS]
Ritsu's been hacked!
[NAGISA]
He's coming.
[RYUNOSUKE]
Huh?
[NAGISA]
I can't make him out.
What the--?
How is he doing that?
Take him down!
Dumbass is walking
right into us!
[REAPER] Hand-to-hand
combat was the first skill
I honed as an assassin.
So as you might imagine,
I'm rather good at it.
A talent 99% unnecessary
in this profession,
but without it, 1% of
my quarry would survive.
If you want to be a killer,
it's an indispensable tool.
Take my word for it.
[REAPER]
Ah, females are so fragile.
Don't expect me to handle the
rest of you this delicately.
Everyone. Stay back.
Leave this guy to me.
Are you outta your mind?
[NAGISA]
She's all right.
That crunching noise was
the sound of her gear
absorbing the impact.
Still, though.
The Reaper thinks
her ribs are cracked,
which really pisses me off.
[NAGISA]
When I'm like this,
my bloodlust demands
satisfaction for all of us.
[NAGISA]
With these hands...
[gasps]
Whoa!
[KARMA] Well, damn.
This isn't gonna work.
[STUDENTS grunting]
The classic stunner clap.
Yours and Lovro's might
conceivably startle a cat.
But in sufficiently
skilled hands,
the move can accomplish
quite a bit more.
Human consciousness has
a frequency, you see.
The higher the peaks, the more
sensitive one is to stimulus.
When your prey's
in a particularly
agitated state of mind,
a powerful enough sound
wave can work wonders.
[REAPER] Of course, they'll be
startled, but that's hardly all.
Oh, oh no,
the voluntary nervous system
will be temporarily paralyzed.
[NAGISA] This is...
This is top-level stuff.
[REAPER]
Huh. So that's it?
Well, okay then. Except I seem
to be short a few of you.
[MEG gasps]
[MEG]
Professor Bitch!
[OKUDA]
She's still breathing!
You're in charge of
taking care of her.
[TERASAKA] Man, I always get
stuck with the grunt-work.
'Kay.
Let's rendezvous with the others
and get the hell out of here.
Yay! What a relief.
I thought for sure
she was a goner!
Yeah, right?
[thud]
[TOKA]
Um, Professor Bitch?
Ah.
How lovely to finally be myself.
Six whole months asleep before
my prince came to wake me.
Now, then, to put you
brats out of commission.
What're you talking about?
This can't be real.
Time for your final lesson, boys
and girls. I hope you're ready.
Son of a--!
Oh! I stepped on
a rock barefoot.
Jeez. C'mon, miss. Let's--
[OKAJIMA]
Not cool.
[TOKA]
That was a dirty trick.
We were actually worried
about you there for...
Yeah, well,
whad'ya gonna do?
Blame it on the experience gap.
I've seen a little bit more
carnage than you punks.
[REAPER] Already? You took
them out all by yourself.
[IRINA] I was only
following your advice.
There's no point throwing in
with a bunch of
snot-nosed know-nothings.
[REAPER] Glad you've
finally seen the light.
They're only children after all.
For all the good they are to us
they might as well be
from another world.
They breathe clean air,
we breathe blood mist.
[REAPER]
You there. What'll it be then?
Will you come quietly, or stand
your ground in a losing battle.
[TERASAKA groans]
Blah, blah, blah.
Dude, bring it on.
Itona and I'll kick
your crazy ass.
[ITONA]
I surrender.
Huh?
[ITONA]
If we fight, we're toast.
This guy's on a
whole other level.
[TERASAKA]
You're kidding me.
[ITONA] It's like you said.
If we lose today, so what?
All we gotta do is
win once. Be patient.
[KAEDE]
So now what?
[KARMA]
Listen, buddy.
I don't know what your big plan
is for killing Koro-sensei,
but I wouldn't count
on it goin' smoothly.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm a gifted improviser.
That's my job.
I can work with bad
intel as well as good.
Hm?
[IRINA]
Huh?
Karasuma?
[STUDENTS gasp]
[REAPER]
Why is he here?
Pro'ly the Octopus.
He told us once if
there was ever a wall
we couldn't get over...
...he'd take over from there.
We're gonna be okay.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I've got their scent!
Ha-ha! Didn't I tell you?
In this clever canine
disguise, I'm a natural!
There is absolutely
nothing natural
about what you're
doing right now.
[chuckling]