[KUNUDON]
Surprise!
[KIDS]
Hey! It's Kunudon!
Hiya, kids! Are you
ready for this?
[KIDS]
Sir, yes, sir!
Look sharp, it's finals!
The most important
test of the year!
I hope you've studied.
Here at Kunugigaoka Academy,
grades are everything:
and we all know what happens
to boys and girls who fail.
[KIDS]
They become gutter trash!
Speaking of. How to we think
E Class will do on the finals?
[KIDS]
They'll bomb! Hooray!
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI]
The basics, you've got down pat.
No question there.
And if your performance First
Semester is anything to go on,
I believe we can
reasonably expect
your scores to sky rocket!
So what's the deal?
Will it be like last time?
Either we place in the top 50
or you pack it up and go?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nope! With midterms,
I've come to realize my focus
on rank was too shortsighted.
Phooey to that.
Far better that each of you
have individual goals
tailored to affect
personal academic growth.
Therefore, I've devised
the perfect target:
an objective customized
to your needs as assassins.
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not to worry, Terasaka my boy!
Even you can do well
if you believe it!
[TERASAKA groans]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Now, then.
You'll recall Shiro
revealed to us
that the loss of a tentacle
results in diminished speed.
One less appendage
and already the integrity of my
doppelgängers is compromised.
Note that several
of them have now become
childhood versions
of yours truly.
[NAGISA]
'Kay. Seems logical.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Lose another, and presto!
Even more child-clones
thrown into the mix!
Along with fretful parent-clones
struggling to make ends meet.
[NAGISA]
Now it's getting a little sad.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Lose another.
And the father-clone
has walked out,
leaving the poor,
beleaguered mother-clone
to fend for her latchkey
brood however she can.
[NAGISA]
Ugh. Brutal.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The main take away here, class,
is that each tentacle
kerplooied represents
ten percent reduction
in my agility.
Which brings me to
my proposition.
Those of you who get the
highest scores on your final,
and or the best ranking
in each individual subject,
are vouchsafed the right
to obliterate exactly
one tentacle a piece.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI] This is how we
do finals here, boys and girls.
This is the
Assassination Classroom!
Ask yourself.
Are you prepared to inch
ever closer to the grand prize?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[NAGISA]
I've gotta hand it to him.
The one thing Koro-sensei
does better than anything,
is motivate.
[ASANO] Frankly,
your suggestion appalls me.
I'm an educator. I've no vested
interest in seeing E Class fail.
[IRINA] Uh. Well,
obviously, I can see that.
It's this stuffed shirt
who needs convincing.
[ASANO]
Hm. Let me be perfectly clear.
The chief aim
of this institution
is to foster student autonomy.
Our students determine their
own level of achievement.
My role is ancillary.
I do nothing. Only monitor.
[IRINA]
Hard to trust a man
who throws ten-dollar
words in your face.
That crap about "automony." Ugh.
Yeah, well. All we can really do
is hope none of the tricks
he pulls this time are new.
Hey. Since Koro-sensei's
rewarding their test scores
with tentacle-takeouts,
we need to get in there.
What do you think about me
teaching Phys Ed for a while?
C'mon, pweeze!
I could give them an edge!
[KARASUMA]
Stick with Language Arts.
Stop that.
A tentacle for each top
score earned on our final.
I know! It's exciting, huh?
[KARMA]
That's rare.
You're really fired up
about this, aren't you?
Of course! I know science
backwards and forwards.
This is my shot. I finally get
to contribute to the cause!
What's cool is everybody's
good at something on the test.
Koro-sensei'll lose so many
arms he won't have a prayer!
[GROUP]
Hm?
[SUGINO]
It's Shindo.
Hey, what's up?
How's it goin', man?
Heh. Still lickin' your wounds?
Yeah. Hell of a
tournament, huh?
'Member how I said
payback's a bitch?
Best make it to high school so
we can actually go head-to-head.
[SUGINO laughs]
[SUGINO] Doesn't sound like you
hold out a lotta hope for me.
Listen, somethin'
you should know.
Right now, as I'm
talkin' to you,
A Class is holed up in one of
the Main Campus conference rooms
doing an independent study hall.
It's being led by
a bunch of geniuses.
The school's finest.
They're called the Big Five.
[GROUP]
Uh?
[SHINDO] Coming in at second
place on the midterms.
Upwardly mobile,
ruthless multi-national
social networking
conglomerate CEO in training.
Media Club President and
Social Engineer: Teppei Araki!
[SHINDO]
In third place.
Envy of the
Humanities Department,
inimitable wordsmith.
Student Council Secretary
and Perspicacious Poet:
Ren Sakakibara!
[SHINDO]
In fifth place.
A true sorcerer of science,
consumed by fantasies of
retribution against Akabane.
Biology Club President:
Natsuhiko Koyama!
In sixth place, an infamous
wit who sharpened his tongue
on West Coast vernacular
while kicking it in LA.
Student Council Meeting
Leader: Tomoya Seo!
Um, quick question, dude.
What're you doing
with your voice?
[SHINDO]
Oh, I've...
...always wanted to be an
announcer. Just practicing.
Anyway, lording over all these
guys is the grand overachiever.
[STUDENT]
We are the best and brightest.
The sun around which the
entire student body orbits.
Alas, storm clouds are moving
in, ladies and gentlemen,
casting their pall over
our brilliance from below.
We know E Class
attempted to scratch
and bite their way into the top
fiftieth percentile on midterms.
Now that finals are upon us,
measures must be taken to
drive the Untouchables out.
We must see to it that
the storm clouds evaporate.
That our incandescence
slices through.
Who's with me?
[STUDENTS cheering]
[SHINDO]
In first place,
hoisting his flag on the top
spot of the National Mock Exams
with perfect score
in every subject,
the man with a genetic
disposition to lead.
Student Council President:
Gakushu Asano!
[SUGINO]
The principal's only son.
Mr. President,
about question three.
Ah. That is a puzzler.
Try again. Be sure to
complete the square first.
You know the axis equation.
X equals A, so.
Oh! Of course!
[SHINDO] You gotta figure
high scores are a given
with this bunch.
The head honchos have ambition,
charisma, reputations to uphold.
And above all, the desire
to keep you down.
You know this.
If you place the particle
after this word,
the meaning of the sentence
changes completely.
But you wanna be careful.
Pronouns and how they're
used should change
depending on the speaker.
Come on! This
isn't rocket science!
I've seen babies more
eloquent than you.
This single innovation
affected fundamental change
across the whole field
of information theory.
Are you even listening?
Don't assume this
won't be on the exam!
What's the matter,
head gettin' full?
This is O-Chem. Memorization
is your only hope! Ah!
Asano has perfect
scores in every subject.
The other four are experts, man.
You can't be messin' around.
It's serious business.
They're hardcore.
They don't want you guys
back on the Main Campus.
It's a point of pride.
Thanks for the tip, Shindo.
They don't have
to worry for now.
We're not looking to go back.
It's kind of personal. I'd
explain, but I really can't.
Let's just say, uh...
Beating A Class is
in our best interest.
We're fighters. You know this.
Hm. More power to ya.
Just remember, this is your
fight, so leave me out of it.
[OKAJIMA]
Yeah...
[KAEDE]
First in every subject?
[NAGISA laughs nervously]
[ISOGAI]
Hey, guys! Wait up!
[NAGISA]
What's goin' on?
[ISOGAI] You wanna hit the books
at the Main Campus library
tomorrow after class?
I reserved us a spot.
Actually, been holdin'
on to this for a while.
Normally, we're dead last
on the waiting list,
so, this little miracle
is like a platinum ticket.
--[NAGISA, KAEDE] Count us in!
--[NAKAMURA] Me, too!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Look at how fired up they are.
It was certainly worth putting
my tentacles on the line.
[GAKUSHU]
Yes, sir.
As instructed, I've raised
the bar considerably
with regards to
A Class's test scores.
I trust that you're satisfied?
[ASANO]
Sadly... no.
I require results, young man.
A status report in and
of itself is meaningless.
You know as well as I,
excellence is not rewarded
so much as expected, son.
If you and your classmates
rank in the top 50
and secure the top spot
in all subjects, you pass.
[GAKUSHU] All to keep the E
Class upstarts firmly in line.
I understand the principle
all too well, forgive the pun.
Why you cling to it
is somewhat lost on me.
Yes, granted, their grades
may be on the upswing,
but they can only get so far.
They won't trump their
betters. It's unthinkable.
Don't let that confidence
be your undoing, my boy.
Things change.
The scales can tip in favor
of the rabble in an instant.
The elite do well to take heed.
Those at the top must
mind their balance.
An excellent point
very well made.
I'll see to it that we get
results, sir. You may rest easy.
One more thing.
A simple question.
Not asking as a student,
but as your son.
Oh, dear. I do hope you don't
expect special treatment.
[GAKUSHU]
No, no, wouldn't dream of it.
It's just simple curiosity.
What is it about E Class?
It's almost like you
have something to hide.
[ASANO grunts]
[GAKUSHU] You haven't
raised an idiot, father.
Any fool can see the
idlers have more claim
to your attention these days
than in years previous.
Hard as it is
to give credit to,
I just can't shake the idea
that you're involved
in something shady.
Rumors of strange happenings.
Eye-witness accounts of
a flying yellow octopus.
A ridiculously disguised man
buying large amounts
of junk food.
Well-endowed coeds hearing
suggestive disembodied whispers.
[ASANO]
Huh.
What gives? Mass hallucinations,
or something else?
[ASANO]
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were digging for
something to use against me.
Why on earth would I do that?
But you could hardly
blame me if I were.
I am your protégée.
[ASANO chuckles]
Nice touch, indeed. Spoken
like a well-trained dog.
[GAKUSHU laughs]
[GAKUSHU]
Careful.
One day the master might
find himself on the leash.
[ASANO laughs]
[ASANO] Or the dog might find
himself in thrall to his master
as a corporate slave
till the day he dies.
[BOTH chuckling]
[ARAKI] Well, look at that.
It's the E Class crew.
Why even bother? This
place is wasted on you.
Pearls before swine,
as the saying goes.
[NAKAMURA]
Ugh. Don't tell me.
[KAEDE]
The Big Five.
How cute. They're studying.
Hey, scrubs, playtime's over.
The big kids need their spot.
Hey! Do you mind?
We're trying to fill our
heads with knowledge!
[NAGISA]
Um, Kayano.
We're not going anywhere.
We reserved these
seats in advance.
Ah. Yeah. You don't
know what it is
to study in air-conditioning
till you don't have it.
Move along, please.
Well what do we
have here, fellas?
Are the hard-luck cases
defying their betters now?
I mean, I knew they were
stupid, but this is a new low.
Hey! He said these were ours!
What?
[OKUDA] You're not the only ones
allowed to have good grades!
Everyone has a right to
them if they work hard.
Try bossing us around when we
kick your butts on the finals.
[NAGISA]
Whoa. Okuda.
You sure have gall talkin' like
that to me, you little twerp!
And nice glasses by the way,
they make you look
like a total nerd!
Ha! Am I right?
Uh. I guess?
[SAKAKIBARA]
Don't be so quick to judge.
[ARAKI]
Huh?
Look at her.
Oh, my, pearls before
swine, indeed.
Hey there. Something tells me
you're the sort of woman who
gets her thrills from a sonnet.
You make me wonder if my
standards aren't too high.
Um. Could you get out
of my ear, please?
[NAGISA, KAEDE] She attracts
the worst kind of guys.
[KOYAMI] Wait a minute.
I know who these kids are.
[KOYAMI] Yukiko Kanzaki,
ranked 23rd in Japanese.
Rio Nakamura, ranked
11th in English.
Yuma Isogai, ranked 14th
in Social Studies.
Manami Okuda, 17th in Science.
Oops, sorry!
Turns out these aren't your
average everyday dumbasses.
They actually have
some academic chops!
[ARAKI] Is that a fact?
How interesting.
Well, as long as we're all here,
why not make it
even more interesting
and wager those chops
against stakes higher
than bragging rights?
Whoever scores lower has to
do what the other class says.
Sound fun?
C'mon, don't be a wuss.
Where the hell's that
attitude all of a sudden?
If you wanted to, we'd even
put our lives on the line.
I'd be more careful about
betting my life if I were you.
Ha! You don't scare me!
We have ourselves a deal, kid!
You don't even know what
we're gonna make you guys do
when you lose!
Don't try backin' out now.
[ARAKI]
You'll regret this!
[NAGISA] Well, we just
opened up a can of worms.
Wait till everyone else
catches wind of this.
[SEO]
I-I know it was stupid, but...
Look, I was only tryin'
make a point, okay?
C'mon. I never thought they'd
actually take us up on it.
[GAKUSHU] It's all right.
You're not in trouble.
In fact, this might be a good
way to inspire A Class.
[GROUP sighs]
But for now, let us focus
on clarifying the terms.
We don't want
confusion down the road.
I propose the winners
be allowed only one demand.
To be specified after
finals are done.
[ARAKI, SEO]
Hm?
Not to rock the boat,
but seriously? Only one?
Yeah, not a lot
we can do with that.
[STUDENTS gasping]
Oh, I believe there's quite
a lot we can do with that.
If the demand is this...
[GAKUSHU]
Signing a contract that pledges
their total subjugation to
us in 50 separate clauses.
Upon observance
of full compliance,
the constituents of A Class
agree to act as role models
for the constituents of E.
Classic "Status
of Forces" agreement.
[KOYAMI laughing]
One demand encompassing
50 lined items of servitude!
Sounds like a
win-win to me, boss!
Not bad.
Did you just come up with all
these off the top of your head?
You're terrifying, man.
What do you mean by that?
I'm a little hurt.
I'm just a student
humbly exercising his autonomy
in a nurturing environment.
Nothing scary about
that, in the least.
If my grasp of civil law is such
that I know how to crush a man,
what of it?
[ALL gasp]
[GAKUSHU]
Right.
The point I'm laboring
toward is this.
When we play, we play for keeps.
In school, as in life,
there is one rule.
Only the weak show mercy.
Our job is to light the way.
Let's show them all
what the game is about!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[SEO]
You have to give the guy credit.
He knows how
to rally the troops.
Is he a hypocrite? Yes.
Can we see through
him? Of course.
Do we go along with the
bastard anyway? Absolutely.
He's the undisputed heavy
weight champ of coercion.
Gakushu Asano.
I don't think there's anyone
in this school who can beat him.
[yawning]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Blast it all, Karma!
Wake up and get
with the program!
Apply yourself,
for heaven's sake!
You could get the
best overall score!
Calm down, Teach.
You an' I both know
I'm gonna do fine.
My laziness is a credit
to your study method.
We can both afford to relax.
You especially right now.
I mean, look at yourself.
You're startin' to come off
like a regular teacher.
Uptight and boring.
[KARMA] We've already got
a plan of attack, right?
You should have a
little more faith in it.
Are you that worried
about A Class winning this?
Why should we worry?
C'mon, man. We're us.
We've got absolutely nothin'
to lose. What can they do?
If we win, they'll do
whatever we tell 'em to.
I vote we force 'em to
let us use the cafeteria.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] Not a bad
idea, but what about this?
I say force them to relinquish
their pride and joy.
[OKANO]
The school pamphlet?
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI] You're already
well acquainted with being
the low man on the totem pole,
but I want you to
experience what it's like
to fight one's way,
tooth and nail,
all the way to the top!
An assassin aims high
to bring his target low.
[ASANO] My son has stirred
up quite a blood-frenzy
among his peers.
We must utilize his
ferment to improve
our fine institution's
standard deviation.
Worry not, Principal.
The questions here will
bedevil even A Class.
Ha! My best work.
Concentrated nuggets of
specialized knowledge, these.
Oh-ho!
I hesitate to even call them
exam questions at this stage.
No!
They've become conundrums!
Riddles! Outright beasts!
[ASANO]
Satisfactory.
No doubt they will inspire.
[GAKUSHU] Nested among
reams of legal jargon
hides an item of
special interest.
A sub-clause forbidding E Class
from keeping even
the tiniest of secrets.
Whatever you're trying
to smokescreen, father,
don't think I won't find it.
Once they've signed this,
the E Class dolts will be
a cinch to shake down.
Soon, I'll have uncovered
your biggest weakness.
You'll be at my mercy.
And we all know you're
thoughts on that subject.
All right, Nagisa.
You ready to kick ass or what?
I guess. If the test is fair.
Hey, hey! A tad more
confidence, please!
We're shootin' for the
top spot on this baby,
so don't mess up!
[TAKADA]
This is gonna be hysterical.
Ha! The rumors true?
You make a bet with A Class?
I wonder if you
morons appreciate
what you've gotten
yourselves into.
Oh, look. Cool. We're first.
[NAGISA]
Uh?
[NAGISA, NAKAMURA]
Who's that?
[KARASUMA]
Ritsu's proxy.
Yeah, I know.
The Principal said
an AI taking the finals
was against testing protocol.
Hey, at least the man was okay
with us using a stand-in.
Ever have to deal with
him giving you that look?
You know the one,
right? It's so...
I don't know. It's like he can't
even be bothered to pity you.
Makes you feel
like a damn child.
[NAGISA, NAKAMURA]
Thanks for dealing with him!
Anyway, Ritsu and I have a
li'l message for you guys.
Do your best.
You got it.
[GAKUSHU]
Let the battle begin.
I won't lose. I don't lose.
[NAGISA] Here we go. Things
are about to get interesting.
What's cool is while we're
taking the exams separately,
we're all in this together.
There are the people
we fight alongside of.
The people we fight.
The ones who want us to lose,
the ones who want us to win,
almost feels like an arena.
[CROWD cheering]
[NAGISA]
We might be assassins,
but right now, we have
to fight like gladiators.
[NAGISA]
Another day, another bell.
[BEAST roaring]
[NAGISA]
Round one... begin!