From behind at
point-blank range?
[NAKAMURA]
Like a bolt of lightning
outta the clear blue sky.
Where in the world
has he been hiding?
[KARMA]
Of course.
He was shadowing Mr. Karasuma,
blending in with his
Self-Defense Force camo.
Waiting to pick us off from
the ideal sniper's nest.
[MAEHARA]
Gotcha!
This is exactly why being
around Nagisa has me on edge.
I guess it's one-on-one now.
Fine by me.
Let's finish it.
[SUGINO] So it comes down
to Nagisa versus Karma.
Ballsy tactic.
The kid essentially
used Karasuma
as his own personal blind.
[KORO-SENSEI]
A referee goes largely unnoticed
on the playing field.
Nagisa honed in on that fact,
made himself invisible.
Brilliant!
He waited for the perfect
moment to reveal himself.
His instincts are that
of a natural-born killer.
It's not wise to underestimate
Karma, though.
Comparing these two on the basis
of academic performance,
he soundly beats Nagisa
in every area of study.
That said, the fact
must've dawned on him.
When it comes to
matters of assassination,
Nagisa is, without question,
Karma's greatest adversary.
[KARMA]
Damn. He's already moved.
Nagisa! Put down the
gun and come on out!
We'll settle this with blades!
[gasps]
No way! Don't be an idiot!
Take him out while
you've got the shot!
I don't think he's gonna fire.
[NAGISA]
Karma. He always plays so dirty.
If I ignore his challenge
and shoot him right now,
you can bet the red team'll be
hard-pressed to concede defeat.
He's counting on
me to know that.
[NAGISA] If I want everyone on
board with saving Koro-sensei,
this has to play out
on Karma's terms.
I have to beat him
at his own specialty.
Seriously?
No! They're going mano a mano?
It makes sense.
Nagisa respects Karma
in a big way,
and he needs him to understand
where he's coming from.
[OKAJIMA]
Let's move in for a better view!
Not gonna lie.
I'm still for not
killing Koro-sensei,
but... seeing Karma just put
himself out there like that?
When I tagged Rinka,
I felt the same way.
Supposing we wind up
having to kill him,
what would that feel like?
And now we watch
the flip-floppers
crawl out of the woodwork.
Must be some correlation
between strong opinions
and working camouflage, huh?
A class like this
pulls unexpected things
outta everybody.
You, Kayano, Mimura,
and Kanzaki, for example.
Some go berserk.
Some get all fired up
to do better next time.
Some we assume are slackers turn
out to actually have a plan.
Some who pass
themselves off as jokers
turn out to be dead serious.
Oh, shut up.
[TERASAKA]
And weirdest of all,
not only does the
runt of the litter
turn out to be a
genius assassin,
the guy we all thought
this came easiest to
has gotta work his ass off.
So, whoever wins
this has my respect.
With the crazy skillsets we have
as a group, something tells me
we can handle any challenge
that comes our way.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[NAGISA] Ever since we
met as First Years,
to put it simply,
I've looked up to him.
[KARMA]
Excuse me, sir? What's this?
[ONO]
Whoa, Akabane.
That's second-year
stuff you're lookin' at.
[NAGISA] He did whatever
he pleased, without fear.
And he was absolutely brilliant.
[KARMA]
Okay. That's all I needed.
I can handle the rest
on my own, thanks.
[ONO]
Mm?
What? You're kidding me.
By the way, Teach,
I'm just gonna leave now.
[NAGISA]
If only I could be like that.
From where I stood, Karma seemed
to have it all figured out.
[KARMA]
Wait, really?
Nazzoni directed "Sonic Ninja"?
And it's out now?
That's awesome!
Didn't even know.
We should go see it!
Are you cool to come
with me, Shiota?
[NAGISA]
All of a sudden,
we were hanging out
and I felt six feet tall.
That was halfway
through our first year.
Life was good.
[NAGISA] But it wasn't
long before I learned
that all good things
come to an end.
Well, well,
what do we have here?
You beat my good buddy to a
pulp and you're still walkin'.
Huh? Yeah, I s'pose I am.
For the record,
your buddy started it.
He had it comin'.
You're fulla crap!
See, accordin' to him--
Come again, please?
I'm havin' a little trouble
understandin' ya.
[NAGISA]
He could do whatever he pleased
because he had the strength
to back himself up.
[NAGISA]
Not a place I was ever gonna be.
He must've gotten bored sharing
the stage with a nobody.
By the time they suspended him,
we'd gone back to
being just classmates.
[KARMA] He's always been
a harmless little mouse.
A guy with my rep has to be
on high alert around most folks.
Not with him, though.
Looking back on it now,
I'm the one who put
the distance between us.
Even then, there was something
about him that made me nervous.
Now where'd he'd run
off to? Hey, Nagisa!
[KARMA] I could put my
guard down around him.
[gasps]
I've right been here
the whole time.
You didn't see me?
[KARMA] But for some reason,
he had me on edge.
It was like, if he wanted he
could've killed me in my sleep.
Always so sweet
natured and honest.
On the surface, we couldn't
have been more different.
Still... beneath that innocent
façade lurked something else,
something downright sinister.
I wanted to drag it
out of him. Crush it.
Not that there'd have been any
point fighting him in class.
Whatever he has, it's
totally beyond all that.
I couldn't deal. Before long,
we'd drifted apart.
And here we are.
A couple of Third Years
in a class on assassination,
staring each other down.
[NAGISA]
This is it.
The only way to get our
point across is to win.
[BOTH]
You are so going down!
Nagisa.
[KORO-SENSEI]
A desire to win.
To conquer. The all-consuming
competitive streak of youth!
You must forget about
me in this moment.
Clear your minds. It's about
what's in front of you.
We kill!
We save!
I'm surprised a
tackle that well-timed
didn't bring him down.
There's a pretty big
difference in strength
between the two of them.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Indeed.
If one knife connects,
it's a win.
Karma won't hesitate to use
the brief window of time
to his advantage.
Ah, but observe Nagisa closely.
He's carrying a second blade.
[KAEDE gasps]
[KAEDE] You think he'll
try the Clap Stunner?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Unlikely.
Karma will've noticed
the hilt on his leg.
The second blade won't
come as a surprise.
Two assassins, their weapons
and methods worlds apart.
How will this
contest be settled?
Don't touch that dial, folks.
[KARMA]
If I don't wanna get inked,
the trick is to take
the hits like a pro.
[NAGISA]
Now!
[KARASUMA]
Nice. He got his knife away.
[NAGISA]
I've got this!
Both their knives
are out of reach!
Wait, look.
Not the one on his leg!
Ha!
Don't even bother.
The second you go for that
blade, the fight belongs to me.
I'll knock you on your ass
and take my sweet time
with the final blow!
[KARMA]
Hm.
Aw, that's all you got?
Holy crap. He's taking
Nagisa's attacks on purpose.
His hits have gotta be having
some kind of effect, right?
I mean, he's been upping his
game for a whole year now.
[KORO-SENSEI] Karma is first and
foremost a combat assassin.
He relishes process:
The bargaining, the strategy.
Only when he's gone
through the moves
will he deal the decisive blow.
Nagisa, on the other hand,
is a pure assassin.
Single-mindedly searching
for the one strike
that will secure victory.
Karma has trained
himself to take a beating.
Hit after hit,
he'll stand his ground and
give as good as he gets.
Should he hold out indefinitely,
Nagisa will have no honorable
choice but to accept defeat.
That was an axe kick!
Bring one of those to the table
and the other guy doesn't
have a chance in hell!
[KARMA]
Let's be real.
There'll never be another
place like this. Not ever.
No one else is gonna let me
be honest about how I feel.
But I will kill him.
'Cause, like it or not,
it's the right thing to do.
[KARMA]
What the--?
That's the last ounce
of strength he's got.
[KORO-SENSEI] He bit his tongue
to keep from dropping!
[KARMA]
Go for it, Nagisa.
Come at me with all that
natural talent I never had.
I'll break you over
my knee like a twig.
This game is mine.
It's all channeled
into that blade.
Dodge, and his bloodlust
will dissolve.
[KARMA]
What the--?
What's he doing?
[NAGISA yells]
A triangle choke!
With his carotid cinched,
it's only a matter of time
before he passes out.
Nagisa's choke hold is even more
effective than it was earlier.
[groaning]
Ugh.
You are going to hear me out!
Look at 'im!
How the hell is he
pinning him down like that
in the first place?
[KORO-SENSEI]
The element of surprise.
Nagisa sacrificed his greatest
skill to create a red herring,
opting to finish with
a martial arts move.
All to make a simple point:
Karma's own specialty
has, in the end,
been turned against him.
[KARMA] Exactly like
I tried to do to him.
Playing by my terms,
he's making it impossible for
anyone to contest the outcome.
Ugh. Damn it.
At this rate, I'm toast!
[gasps]
He's got a knife!
[KAEDE]
Oh no!
[NAGISA]
No, I can't fight.
I'm probably way too big
of chicken to even try.
Uh, unless it was absolutely
a matter of life and death.
I give up.
Uncle. Uncle.
You win, Nagisa. Good job.
[KARMA groans]
[yells]
[KARMA]
Are you listening to me?
That's enough!
Red Team has surrendered.
Game over.
Blue Team is the winner!
[BLUE TEAM]
Yeah!
Okay. Cool.
You worked hard for
that win, Nagisa.
I actually... won?
I beat Karma?
'Fore you start doin'
a little victory dance,
let's make one thing
perfectly clear.
You left your back
wide open to attack.
I just couldn't bring
myself to stab you.
Talk about bein' stuck between
a rock and hard place.
No one would've been satisfied
with me winning that way.
Can't believe you managed
to get the drop on me
with martial arts.
Seriously, dude,
who'd have ever thought I'd be
beaten at my own game like that?
[sighs]
You killed me.
Right, you wanna
save Koro-sensei?
Talk. I'm listenin'.
Are you really? No joke?
Quit starin' at me like that.
You look like mousetrap cheese.
I've seen fewer bruises
on a week-old peach.
Wow,
even in defeat you can't bear
to waste a single insult, huh?
Good ol' Karma.
[KARMA]
Please.
Look. Why don't we drop
all the back-and-forth?
I'm really not feelin'
it after that fight.
So what? We talk to each
other like human beings?
Feels kinda weird
after all this time.
[KARMA]
Fine.
I'll start us off.
Gimme your hand... old friend.
Thanks, Karma.
Old friend.
[KORO-SENSEI]
True feelings tend to bubble up
when under pressure
from a big decision.
Often as not, there's conflict.
But look. In the end,
harmony reigns.
Because these boys and girls
have fought in earnest.
they've come to
see and appreciate
one another's true feelings.
[NAGISA]
...pull your punches, Karma.
[KARMA] Only because I didn't
want to paralyze ya.
[KORO-SENSEI] Sometimes conflict
can be the best opportunity
to strengthen a friendship.
[KARASUMA]
Is that another lesson?
Without strife, we can't grow
or learn a damn thing?
[chuckling]
[KARASUMA] I'm sure you all have
your own thoughts on the matter.
I for one have no objection
to the course this
class has chosen.
That said,
I can only allow you to try
to save him on one condition.
You have until the end of
the month to figure out a way.
You might be taking a
break from assassination,
but many others involved aren't.
Their efforts are in full swing.
If it turns out he
needs to be killed,
I believe you should
be the ones who do it.
Make me a promise.
However January plays out,
February onward, you'll focus
on the original objective.
Whether you save or kill,
give it all you've got.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[TAKEBAYASHI]
To put this in general terms...
...what about world leaders?
Is assassinating Koro-sensei
their only game plan?
I doubt it.
Bear in mind,
the larger goal is to save the
Earth from certain destruction.
They can't afford
to be unilateral.
Odds are they've
explored options
that don't involving
killing him.
Why don't we look into what
those options might be?
He's right.
There're research facilities
all over the world
dedicating themselves
to the problem 24/7.
Needless to say, their
work is highly classified.
Finding out what they know
will be next to impossible.
Infiltration of the
project database complete!
[KARASUMA]
What the--?!
[RITSU] If it's online,
I can access it. No problem.
What can I say? I've learned
a lot in the last year.
Nice job.
[ISOGAI]
Wow.
Every lab in existence
has to be on this thing.
Jackpot!
[RITSU]
Uh-oh.
I've combed through
all the files,
but I'm not seeing any trace
of the information we need.
[ISOGAI] I guess the
higher-ups only hand off
that kinda stuff in person.
[MAEHARA]
Great.
So is anybody even
doing research
on how to save Koro-sensei?
Guys, look. There's
a lab in the U.S.
"Preventing destructive
antimatter chain reactions
due to tentacle-cell
aging and fission."
I'm no scientist, but that
seems like a definite hit to me!
"Last samples return from
ISS on January 25th."
What is ISS? Anybody know?
Wait a minute. That's...
Whoa!
The International Space Station!
They're conducting their
research in outer space!
Um, it's possible!
Certain types of research
require zero gravity
or a perfect vacuum.
And, well, of course,
if there's a chance it
could cause a big, uh,
catastrophic explosion,
there'd way be way less
collateral damage.
[ISOGAI] Couldn't we just ask
for the data as colleagues?
You could, sure.
But sadly you kids are just
one outpost among many.
With all the red tape involved,
that data might
not make it time.
Mr. Karasuma.
[BOTH]
Uh?
[KARMA]
I know what you're thinking.
Killing him is still
the backup plan.
Trust me. We're not going
to go into this half-cocked.
If there's any hope
of saving him at all,
we'll do whatever it takes.
If not, this class will stick
to the original game plan.
Won't we, Nagisa?
[NAGISA]
Mm.
That's been our understanding
from the start.
Before we do anything,
I need a blueprint.
Be square with us.
How serious are the rules
we're about to break?
[KURASAMA grumbles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mr. Karasuma. Miss Irina.
Will you give the students
and I a moment?
What we're about to discuss
might potentially cause
one or two liability
issues for you.
Okey dokey!
Here's essentially what
you're trying to do.
You need to grab a quick peek
of the research data in question
before it reaches America
from Outer Space.
Yeah, but as for the how...
[KORO-SENSEI]
How indeed!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Lookie, lookie!
Guess where this beautifully
streamlined bucket of bolts
is about to be sent?
Is that a manned rocket?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Precisely!
A proof-of-concept craft
developed right here in Japan.
Test dummies have been given the
honor of taking the first trip.
But what if they were
replaced with actual people?
[STUDENTS gasp]
You're serious...
[chuckles] That's it.
Our teacher's officially
gone off the deep end.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes!
Consider this the
Assassination Classroom's
out-of-season research project!
Ground control to Major Tom:
The ISS has been hijacked!
[NAGISA]
Whoa. No way.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes, way! All the way!