[NAGISA] "Spear of Heaven."
"Shield of Earth."
In a desperate,
last ditch effort
to assassinate Koro-sensei,
the government went high tech.
We'd been pushed aside.
Given absolutely no say.
Okay then, everybody.
Moment of truth.
Our final mission!
[NAGISA] We need to see him.
This can't end until we do.
[NAGISA] Countdown to
Koro-sensei's deadline,
approximately... three hours.
[COMMANDER] The Spear of
Heaven will be fully charged
in about three hours.
Shame that magnificent
bastard'll be obliterated
so completely.
Seems a waste of
good test samples.
The things we do in the
name of world peace.
Do the kids have a chance?
Can they pull it off?
[KARASUMA grumbles]
[beeping]
[BOTH gasp]
[COMMANDER]
Report.
There's an intruder
on the mountain, sir.
[SOLDIER A] Someone's gotten
past the police line.
[SOLDIER B]
It's more than one!
[SOLDIER B screaming]
[SOLDIER C]
This is a nightmare!
I can't get a visual
on how many!
Think you can mess with us?
Way to go. Good
teamwork, you three.
[SOLDIER D]
We've lost comm with B Squad.
Sonsabitches are the
real deal. Stay alert.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir.
[SOLDIER E yelps]
What the hell?
[SOLDIER D]
We've got a sniper!
Our position is compromised!
Send reinforcements!
[crack]
Uh, okay. That didn't really
sound so good for him.
[SUMIRE]
He's fine.
No, honest. All I
did was wrap him up.
This squad's been
neutralized, we're good.
[KARMA]
Nice.
[RYUNOSUKE]
How're things by you?
[KARMA]
Hm?
At the moment...
[screams]
My sinuses are on fire!
[KARMA] Sorry, soldier. But
hey, look on the bright side,
this is a testament
to how difficult it is
to make you scream.
[SOLDIER C screaming]
Come on, man.
I've gotta lure your buddies
here somehow, don't I?
I think I can take
down two or three more.
Hey, Ritsu, what're
the odds on that?
[RITSU]
Good.
At least three more
approaching over the ridge.
They've got a fixed machine
gun on the high ground.
It's stationed over
by the fir trees.
Roger that.
So if we cut a path through
the crimson-glory vines
out past the stone oaks,
we should be set?
[RITSU]
Yep. That oughta get you there.
Terasaka, you're up next.
Head that direction
and take 'em out.
Advance your team
to the lone pine.
[TERASAKA]
Copy that!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[EMPLOYEE A]
Squads C and D are MIA!
[EMPLOYEE B]
Status report, now!
Damn it, Karasuma. What is this?
Those boys and girls
know the mountain
like the backs of their hands.
It's their turf. Where they've
spent most of the past year.
What do you expect?
You've never set foot
in this place before.
They know their own hunting
ground better than you.
On this patch of
campus backwoods,
they're the most terrifying
assassins imaginable.
Ah! You put them up
to it, didn't you?
[KARASUMA]
I did nothing of the sort.
They make their own decisions.
Believe me when I say
they're more than able
to operate on their own.
I've learned from experience
not to hold them back.
They'll get the best of
you every single time.
[growls]
[IRINA]
Spoken like a proud papa.
[KARMA]
All right, Okajima, I'm there.
About another 50 meters.
[KARASUMA] Karma Akabane.
Easily the best suited to lead.
He's the brains of this
outfit, you can be sure.
Mind like a steel trap.
[SOLDIER H] Oh God!
How many of them are there?
[SOLDIERS grunting]
Cool. We'll just give
you a li'l taze.
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[HINANO] How much are we loving
all these booby traps right now?
We set 'em for Koro-sensei,
but they work just
as good on people.
[SOLDIER K]
Ah! Hey! Let me down!
[TERASAKA] Tch. Guess there's
a few of you jokers still left.
[CAPTAIN]
Congratulations.
You caught us
with our pants down.
I'd say you've got this
neck of the woods down
better 'n we do if it
weren't so obvious--
Really? Stun darts?
Thing is, once you know
what you're up against,
turnin' the tables
ain't nothin'.
[ALL gasp]
[SUGINO]
Karma!
Little punks.
Listen, if you just
behave, this can be over,
and nobody has to get hurt.
What's the point of rebelling
this late in the game?
Give it up already!
[KANZAKI]
One way or another,
we're gonna see this thing
through to the end!
[TERASAKA] You don't get to
march in at the last minute
and tell us what to do!
[ISOGAI]
You have to trust us!
We know how to
handle Koro-sensei!
[MAEHARA] Stand down and
let us do this our way!
[CAPTAIN]
Huh?
Karma!
[KARMA chuckles]
[KARMA]
Nagisa.
[KAEDE] Heads up!
The guy's still moving!
Stupid teenagers.
[screaming]
Hey, dumbasses, what do
you think you're doin'?
Finish what you started
instead of high fiving
each other like losers!
[EMPLOYEE D] None of the
troops are responding, sir.
[COMMANDER]
Damn it.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I thought that sounded like you.
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
You've come so far. Look at you.
[STUDENTS shouting]
Those students
crossed the barrier
knowing full well the danger
they'd be up against?
What was this stunt
supposed to accomplish?
We can't just leave a group of
civilians to their own devices.
If the target feels cornered,
things could get desperate.
We don't want the situation
to get any worse.
May I suggest you send us in?
Irina and I have experience
dealing with these kids.
[IRINA]
Bleh.
[MEG]
The laser's almost charged up.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So it would seem.
I imagine they'll probably
try firing the killing shot
just shy of midnight.
There's enough concentrated
power in that baby
to shut down even my
Absolute Defense Form.
What do we do?
We have to leave! Let's try
to find a way out of here!
Oh, I know! You could take us
as hostages or something!
[STUDENTS grunt]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm sorry, children.
There's no stopping this now.
Too many people are
aware of my existence.
You knew it'd come
to this eventually.
You knew it all along.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Even if I don't explode,
the cat's out of the bag.
We'd be fools to think
the world would accept
the existence of
something like me.
Sooner or later, they'll
want me out of the picture.
It's a perfectly
reasonable reaction.
You can't tell me we wouldn't
have found a way around all that
if we'd acted sooner.
We could've busted up
the barrier protectors.
Gone on TV to try
and make our case.
[KORO-SENSEI]
You'd have met with resistance.
The public would decry
you as dangerous.
Possibly demand you to
be put under surveillance.
And besides, the projectors'
defenses are impregnable.
If I so much as
chuck a rock at them,
the answer is
anti-aircraft artillery.
Likely as not,
even given your skill,
you would've been captured.
That's the level
of sophistication
we're looking at here.
No expense was spared.
No technical
innovation overlooked.
In a very real way,
my assassination represents
the many disparate threads
of mankind's cumulative
wisdom brought together
for a single purpose.
What an accomplishment!
In truth, I'm honored.
[NAGISA gasps]
So then, you're saying all the
hard work we put into this...
...has been for nothing?
[KORO-SENSEI] Come now, Yada.
I hardly think that's fair.
Think about it.
You've journeyed to outer space,
uncovered vital information,
surely we don't call
that "nothing"?
Especially when said information
brought our classroom a
much-needed ray of light.
The past month may
have been short,
but also uncommonly sweet.
That's what it's all about.
The hard work gave you heart.
And you used every bit
of what you've learned
to come and see me
one last time.
For a teacher, there is
no greater happiness.
[TERASAKA]
So time's up, is that it?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mew?
The risk is still less
than one percent!
And I don't care
what other people say!
I'll take those odds any day!
We've been a hell
of a lot closer to you
than any of the jerks
runnin' this show.
They have an obligation
to hear us out!
The Octopus isn't dangerous!
He's a pervert, sure,
but he's not dangerous!
As far as they're concerned,
we're in over our heads.
Why give delinquents
the time of day, right?
It's much easier
to brush us off.
Like we're just gonna
take it?! Bullshit!
Next government suit
crosses my path--
[ALL gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Terasaka, all of you.
Permit me to give you
a word of advice.
In life, we travel upstream,
thrashing against the
mighty current of society.
More often than not,
things simply won't
pan out as you wished.
Don't apportion blame.
Society is in a
circumstance of its own.
Resist the temptation
to renounce it.
Believe me, your time and energy
are far better
channeled elsewhere.
When hardship prevails,
say, "That's life,"
and marshal your dignity towards
navigating the disappointment
as best you can.
When the water calms,
ask yourself:
If society tosses me about
like a piece of driftwood,
is it wiser to stay the course,
or find another way?
If E-Class has taught
you nothing else,
take this to heart.
In the Assassination
Classroom...
...you don't have to face
hardships head-on.
You can run. You can hide.
Launch a sneak attack,
if it's not against the rules.
Avail yourself of
unconventional methods.
Whatever you choose, above
all else, be determined.
Don't give frustration
the last word.
The beauty of trial and error
is that there's always hope!
Never forget.
When the moment calls
for a decisive strike,
you are an assassin!
Ugh. Unbelievable.
Of all the times to lecture.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] What can I say?
A lesson seemed appropriate.
A good educator never passes up
an opportunity to teach.
Thank you.
Your rescue efforts move me more
than you could possibly know.
I'm embarrassed to admit that
I've been holding back tears.
Aren't I a mess?
[NAGISA] How... How can
he be so composed?
I don't... I mean,
if he'd never come here,
he might've been able
to lead a normal life.
[NAGISA]
It's us. We were the reason.
[KORO-SENSEI]
By the way, Nakamura.
I couldn't help but notice how
delicately you carried yourself
during that last battle.
And, uh, do I smell
something sweet, by chance?
[NAKAMURA] Your ears are
as sharp as your nose.
It's been exactly one year to
the day since the moon blew up.
And if I remember correctly,
Miss Yukimura designated
today as your birthday.
Yeah, it's no big
deal, but, I mean,
if you wanna shower
me with praise
for getting it here intact,
then I guess-- Uh, hey!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sorry,
but this is my first
taste of sweet in a week!
[NAKAMURA] Don't you
dare get your drool on it!
Ugh. So gross!
All right guys, let's sing!
And go!
[STUDENTS]
♪ Happy Birthday to you! ♪
--♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
--[TERASAKA] Dude.
--Do we even have the rights
--♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
--to this song? Er! You!
[STUDENTS] ♪ Happy birthday,
dear Koro-sensei. ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you! ♪
[STUDENTS cheering]
[KORO-SENSEI]
My wish already came true.
C'mon! Blow out the candles!
[KORO-SENSEI]
A far greater reward
than I could ever deserve.
[SHIRO]
And many more.
Shiro!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yanagisawa.
The hour is upon us.
So then, permit me
to give you the gift
of the world's cruelest death.
[VOICE]
Hello, there.
You do know who I am,
don't you sir?
[SHIRO]
I should reintroduce him
for the benefit
of your students.
This, boys and girls,
is the pupil who stole the name
Reaper from your teacher.
As of today...
[SHIRO] ...I take the liberty
of christening him the new,
and vastly improved,
Koro-sensei!
[whimpering]
[REAPER]
Shame you never really knew me.
Maybe another time.
It's been fun, though.
[KORO-SENSEI] I thought
if I could pass my skills
on to an apprentice,
the scope of my work
would broaden.
And, well, he volunteered so
eagerly, how could I not accept?
Here was a boy
who coveted power.
So power I taught
him, in spades.
To inspire loyalty,
I emphasized the chasm
between our respective gifts.
I gave him profit and
awe in equal measure.
Betrayal ought not
have been possible.
Master, I've looked over the
infiltration route for this job.
I say we take the east side.
Fewer guards there.
It'll be much easier.
I'm happy to do
the prep work for us.
Couple of minor tweaks
ought'a do the trick.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hm... I don't think so.
We'll stick to the
plan as-is, thank you.
Master, I've come up
with a knife move
that's guaranteed
to spill blood!
It's a dual-wield variation
on your own signature meth--
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mm. Not terribly effective.
Unless you want the
blood spilt to be your own,
master the method I
actually taught you.
[KORO-SENSEI] I shouldn't
have been so hard on him.
Truly, I shudder to think
how much I didn't know.
He wanted your approval.
Everything he did was just
to get your attention.
Believe me.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm sorry.
You were the first student
I took under my wing...
...and I never gave you credit.
[EXECUTIVE] Yanagisawa.
Why is he here all of a sudden?
Tell me this is
part of the plan.
Well, this does give
us the opportunity
to collect combat data.
Not to mention a body.
A single specimen would win
the war on terror overnight.
[EXECUTIVE]
An invincible killing machine.
The list of practical
applications
is virtually endless.
What's that?
No, seriously? Oh crap!
[NAGISA] Reaper 2.0.
The one who attacked us.
[MURAMATSU] Okay, before
it was just his face,
but now his entire body
freaks me the hell out!
[SHIRO] He underwent
the same modifications
as your precious Octopus.
With one difference.
Quite unlike Itona and
my would-be sister-in-law,
he begged for them.
Far be it from me to judge,
but I think that puts
him a cut above.
I know! Wrap your
head around that.
A man able to overwhelm
you in human form
now possesses unlimited power.
Tentacles fueled by pure hatred.
Can you imagine?
[STUDENT screaming]
[yelling]
[SHIRO]
That was a sonic boom.
His tentacles have an
initial velocity of Mach 20.
Their top speed, however...
...is Mach 40.
How-How is that even possible?
[SHIRO] In short, his basic
performance level is doubled.
The tentacles amplify 2.0's
ungodly kinetic vision
and intuition.
He is readily adaptable
to a supersonic world.
Unlike some people, he took
to his tentacles with ease.
He shares that in common
with version 1.0.
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei!
[SHIRO] The most significant
difference, though,
is that his tentacles,
quite unlike yours and
those of the Octopus,
were designed for sustained use.
He requires no upkeep, rendering
him effectively disposable.
In exchange for being
given three months to live,
he can tap continuously
into unthinkable reservoirs
of strength.
Oh, and his expiration date
does not come with an explosion.
[laughing]
Efficient, deadly,
sustainable, and safe!
[KAEDE] Why do you
always have to do this?
Why do you always
have to hurt people?
Do your own dirty work for once!
You think I'm not willing to?
[MAEHARA, KAEDE gasp]
[SHIRO] You think I'm not
prepared to meet my own demise?
Come now, that's very naive.
What did he just do?
[OKUDA]
Oh no!
I'm beyond giving a damn
whether I live or die.
Everything I cared for was
stolen from me long ago.
I'm merely a collection of
muscle fibers, joints, nerves;
fertile ground for
tentacle implantation.
No, an empty temple where
God-like powers can thrive!
Know this, guinea pig!
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
Your death will
haunt these children
for the rest of their
earthly existence!
[KORO-SENSEI]
What the--?
Listen to me, class.
There's something I neglected
to mention in my earlier lesson.
A clever assassin may avoid
confrontation for a while,
but sooner or later,
the fight will come.
And when it does,
every last ounce of strength
will be put to the test.
In my case, that would be now!