[GAKUSHU]
We worked hard.
I think the results
speak for themselves.
The fall festival was a win.
I'm quite satisfied.
[ASANO]
Oh?
Even with E-Class so close?
Well, sir.
I grant you they entered
with a battle plan...
But in any case winning by a
wider margin would've been--
[ASANO]
Impossible?
[gasps]
[ASANO]
They were running a restaurant.
You're saying there's absolutely
nothing you could've done?
Not even a simple case
of food poisoning?
Come now...
One has to think
outside the box.
[SEO]
Is he serious?
[ARAKI]
What were we supposed to do?
Dip their cookware
in salmonella?
All due respect, sir...
I think your policies
are to blame.
It's all a mystery
to me, but somehow,
E-Class has grown by leaps
and bounds in the past year.
Enough so that they can compete
on the same level as all of us.
More irritating...
Even my own abilities have
increased in parallel.
Spurred by a rivalry I
find rather insulting.
In fact, my min--
Uh... Friends... feel
more or less the same.
This makes no sense.
You were totally about
to call us all minions!
[GAKUSHU]
I can only conclude
that your philosophy is wrong...
Strength isn't relative.
At least, not true strength.
One doesn't develop it
by lording over the weak.
[ASANO]
Excuse me.
Would you mind stepping out
for just a moment, Asano?
I'd like to speak with
your friends alone...
It'll only take about
three minutes or so.
[gasps]
[SAKAKIBARA] Oh, go on.
Don't be like that...
What's three minutes in the
grand scheme of things?
[GAKUSHU]
What're they doing?
[ASANO]
You may come back in now, Asano.
[GAKUSHU gasps]
Ren...! Seo!
[STUDENTS]
Kill E-Class without mercy.
Kill E-Class without mercy...
[GAKUSHU]
What have you done?!
[ASANO] Simply fanned the flames
of their hatred, no more.
A few words is all it takes.
A few whispered truths
to unravel your absurd
idea of strength.
My philosophy, as you call it,
teaches one far less fragile...
Incidentally, I'll be handling
the end-of-term exams myself.
In absence of the weak...
Strength has no meaningful foil.
Let us go back to square one.
[whimpers]
[GAKUSHU] For as far back
as I can remember...
my house has been a classroom...
My father is the teacher.
I'm the student.
Unless there was some lesson
he was eager to drive home,
he and I never said so
much as a good morning.
Driver. Stop the
car immediately.
[DRIVER A]
Sir.
[ASANO]
Hello.
You're doing as well
as ever I see.
This town is about to change;
you feel it in the very air.
In times like these,
men such as me can
make a killing...
No reason not to share
the good fortune.
[HOMELESS GUY A gasping]
[ASANO] For all the gambling
you love so much.
The only real way you can feel
the joy of being alive...
Though of course, I am the
one who taught you that.
[SONOKAWA]
Excuse me?
I can't have heard
you correctly, sir.
I need further compensation.
The clock is ticking, is it not?
Who knows what will happen
before it's all over?
I must consider the risks to
my students, you understand.
One certainly can't expect
secrets to come cheaply.
Keep in mind, the government's
on my turf here.
I can sense that you're moving
forward with some final plan.
This is extortion!
That's enough, Sonokawa.
We can't afford to keep
letting ourselves
be shaken down for hush
money by this man!
By the time March rolls around,
he'll have siphoned off more
than the bounty's worth!
I said enough.
He's entitled to
compensation in exchange
for letting us use his school.
[SONOKAWA growls]
[ASANO]
Quite...
Wire it to my account
if you'd be so kind.
[KARASUMA]
Shrewd instincts, that one.
He even picked up on the
final assassination project
we have in the works.
Well played, principal.
You've got the Defense Ministry
in the palm of your hand.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey-dokey!
Time for an overview of what
we've covered this year!
I hope you're all ready
for the classwork battle!
I assume you'll be aiming
for the top spot, Karma?
I dunno.
Idiots like me have trouble
getting their heads
around the hard stuff.
[KORO-SENSEI] Now, as you know
for the first-term midterms.
I gave all of you the objective
of placing in the top 50.
My apologies for that.
I was too impatient for results.
Nor did I take into account how
gifted your opponents were.
That said,
things are different now.
You've matured in
mind and spirit.
I'm confident the goal I set
for you will be within reach,
whatever the opposition
has in store.
This time you'll place in the
top 50, win your tickets back
to the main campus and,
heads held high,
proudly graduate from
E-Class once and for all!
Wow, you make it
sound so easy...
A-Class has a new teacher
to help 'em prep.
You're not gonna
believe who it is...
I will be personally overseeing
your lessons as of today.
Best of luck, then.
I expect great things.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So we've come to that, have we?
Bad luck for them.
Who wants to be brainwashed
by that creep, am I right?
You guys know what
I'm talkin' about.
The way he can trap you with
that steely-eyed glare.
[SUGINO] But his teaching
methods are hardcore,
and he can't even
move at Mach Twenty.
[ISOGAI] If he's the one
prepping them for the exams,
they've probably already
lost the will to defy him.
[TANAKA groaning]
[OKUNO]
The stuff we're drilling
is ten times easier
than usual...
[FUJII]
...but twenty times faster!
[ASANO] Hashizume, Tanaka,
Fujii, Kondo and Okuno.
You're falling behind.
[HASHIZUME gasps]
[KONDO] How can tell
with his back to us?
Sir! I'm sorry; it's
impossible to keep up!
If we were the Big Five,
maybe, but please!
This is too much!
Impossible, you say?
Perhaps because you don't
know what it means to fight?
Let's have a chat
in the hallway.
Three minutes should do.
Just a little pep talk.
[STUDENTS]
Kill E-Class without mercy!
[ASANO] You do not study for
yourselves, boys and girls...
You study to grow stronger.
To demolish your enemy, E-Class.
When the lower grades
witness your triumph,
they'll be eager to follow
in your footsteps...
They'll know beyond a shadow
of a doubt that you're elite...
and devote themselves
to joining your ranks.
Make no mistake, students;
it's people like you who
push humanity forward...
Ah... Asano, you may leave.
I'd like you to study
on your own at home.
[gasps]
[ASANO]
I'm sure with your skills,
you'll manage to
maintain the top spot.
Provided you keep
your guard up...
I'll see to your classmates.
[FUWA]
When you think about it,
Koro-sensei and the principal
are kind of similar
in a lot of ways.
Like how?
Well, for starters
they both have,
like, extraordinary powers...
And yet they settle
for being teachers.
Seriously, as manipulative
as he is,
the principal could've
easily been Prime Minster
or a business tycoon
or something,
you know?
But here he is, totally devoting
himself to this place.
I mean, it's no wonder
he's such a ruthless guy.
[gasps] Uh. It's Asano.
[MAEHARA]
What the hell do you want?
[SUGINO] Your lackeys too
busy to do recon on us?
It pains me that I
have to say this...
But I have a favor
to ask of you.
[KARMA]
Hm?
[GAKUSHU]
Let me just cut to the chase.
The principal... I need
you people to kill him.
Uh?!
So to speak.
I don't mean something like
murdering him, of course...
That would be patently absurd.
I mean you should
kill his philosophy.
Not sure I understand.
How, exactly?
It's easier than you think.
All E-Class has to do is
dominate the top spots
on the end-of-term exams.
It goes without saying
I'll be placing highest.
Of course, whether or not
I perform as expected
makes no difference.
For detritus like you to
show up A-Class, however...
Now that'd be slap in
the face to his policies.
All right look, we all
know the relationship
between the two of you
isn't really the best.
But he's your dad.
You want to rake his life's
work through the mud?
To reject his legacy?
Oh, on the contrary...
Believe it or not,
my father actually wants
me to take him down.
That's what I've
been groomed to do.
This will be the fulfillment
of his legacy.
That's how we are,
that's what our relationship
is built on.
Then again,
if you didn't know the pleasure
of being raised by him,
let me assure you, his
methods are hell on earth.
That should just about
do it for today, I think.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[ASANO]
Now then. Remember to review.
[STUDENTS]
Kill E-Class without mercy.
[GAKUSHU] The only thing
supporting A-Class right now
is their hatred of you.
He's pushing them
past their limits!
If it raises them to victory
my father's methods will
be the only thing they
trust from here on out.
We can't let that happen.
Hatred only gets you so far.
I know this for a fact.
Scorning one's enemies
is childish.
My flunkies need to learn a
healthy respect for their foes.
Otherwise their strength
will be lopsided,
and I'll only ever be
second in command.
The thing about defeat is that
it gives you new perspective.
So I'm asking you, give
the teacher a lesson.
Let them all know
what it is to lose.
[NAGISA] He may sound
arrogant, but even so,
he's speaking from the
heart... I respect that.
Proud as he is,
he's bowing to us.
Because for once in his life,
he's really worried about
someone other than himself.
Heh.
that's big of you and all,
but lemme tell ya right now,
I'm actually gonna be the
one to take the top spot.
[STUDENTS groan]
What'd I say?
I said next time we weren't
gonna be taking it easy on you.
Prepare to surrender
your throne, Highness.
You're goin' down.
Oh, don't worry, though;
you'll look just as
good in tenth place.
Uh oh!
Guess the gloves are off now!
[TAKEBAYASHI] Just don't let it
turn out like last time, please.
Don't oversell it, man.
Just try to do better than me.
[KARMA grunts]
[TERASAKA groaning]
[ISOGAI]
Asano.
We've been working our
butts off to win all along.
Just like you guys have.
When you get right down to it,
everyone's on the same side.
We're stoked when we win,
frustrated when we lose.
No need for ranks beyond that.
That really should be
enough, don't you think?
E-Class'll strive to
do the best we can.
That way A-Class will
have an opponent
they can be proud to face.
[KARMA] Don't overthink it.
Just bring it on.
Yeah, try to make it fun...
Come at us like
you want us dead.
How amusing...
Very well. I'll fight
with my gloves off, too.
[ONO]
Wait.
All this just for the math
portion of the exam?!
Well the principal did instruct
us to pore through everything
and come up with the
hardest questions.
Ugh! For god's sake,
this is junior high!
What? We're preparing
them for college now?
I understand raising the bar,
but he's out of his mind!
[ASANO]
Ah...
How unusual to see
you here, Koro-sensei.
I'm not aware of having
done anything wrong.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Perish the thought, sir.
You're a by-the-book sort of
man if ever I've seen one.
You wouldn't resort to cheap
tricks this late in the game.
As this will be our final
educational battle,
in a manner of speaking,
I wanted to offer you a
small thanks for accepting
my presence here when you
certainly didn't have to.
[ASANO]
Koro-sensei.
This is your first teaching
position, am I correct?
[KORO-SENSEI]
How did you know that?
[ASANO] Let's call it
educator's intuition, shall we?
It's rather bizarre
you won't divulge
why you chose this profession.
Perhaps you'll do me
the honor after I've won?
[KORO-SENSEI] There's not
much to tell, to be honest.
I can only speak from
experience of course,
but in general there
are only two things
that compel a person to teach,
we wish either to pass
on our successes.
Or, less charitably,
disguise our failures.
Which is it for you I
wonder, Principal Asano?
[ASANO]
Indeed.
[NAGISA] The second-term finals
were only one week away.
Of course, we
studied like crazy.
Anything we didn't understand,
we had Koro-sensei go over.
He did his best to keep up
with our questions, but...
The poor guy's hands
were so full,
his doppelgangers
sorta devolved.
[NAGISA] Then the day
of battle was upon us.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENTS]
Kill E-Class without mercy.
Kill E-Class without mercy...
Yeah, not the biggest fan
of the look in their eyes.
Ignore it. You know they're
just psyching themselves up.
Think you can beat 'em, Karma?
Eh. I dunno.
I mean, if they're planning
to actually kill me,
that might slow me down a tad.
[NAGISA]
The big showdown between
A-Class and
E-Class had come.
Two camps led by two
different monsters.
Hungry...
ready to massacre each other,
on paper, at least.
[NAGISA]
Unless we assassinate this exam,
I don't think we'll be able
to hold our heads high
even if we assassinate
Koro-sensei.
[SUGINO yells]
[NAGISA]
We can do it.
After all, we've learned
from the best.
This is it!
Time to unsheathe
our second blade!
[NAGISA yells]
[ENGLISH BEAST groans]
[NAGISA] We have to show our
true target we're worthy.
Or we can't graduate.
[ENGLISH BEAST groans]
[TEACHER A]
Pencils down.
[panting]
It's no good.
I couldn't get through 'em all.
This is hard!
There's not enough time
to answer every single
little question.
The listening comprehension
part was a beast...
Not even Professor Bitch
would know what all those
vocabulary words meant.
[NAGISA] The first test and
already we're wiped out...
Even worse,
English is my strongest subject.
What the...
Uh-oh...
It's about to get real!
[NAGISA]
Whoa...
Look at that!
The grade-point average on this
thing must be ridiculously low!
Even if even one of us passes,
it'll be nothing
short of a miracle...
What'd we expect, really?
This test is designed
to take us down a peg.
[MAEHARA]
Take that!
[SCIENCE BEAST roars]
[RYUNOSUKE]
So? How's A-Class doing?
[MIMURA] I sneaked a peak
at 'em during the break...
Dude, you talk about seething!
[A-CLASS STUDENTS laughing]
[SCIENCE BEAST groans]
[MIMURA] They were like
blood-crazed animals!
Never underestimate the
power of hatred, I guess.
[NAKAMURA]
Forget that! Just look out!
[OKUDA]
Every man for himself!
[JAPANESE BEAST]
Abunai!
[ALL groaning]
[OKUDA]
Ritsu?
Don't worry; I know what's up.
We land in the top 50 or we're
done, isn't that right?
Who're you?!
Oh...
That's the fake Ritsu.
Bingo.
And the real Ritsu broke
it down for me like so...
Reaching our goal hinges
on low-performers like me
working as hard as we can
to drive up the average
for everybody else.
[MAEHARA]
Hm.
Right, then.
Next round.
[TEACHER A]
Begin!
[TAKEBAYASHI] The questions
are all uncommonly difficult.
And as many as there are
one has to plot out a method
of attack immediately.
Hesitate for even a
fraction of a second,
and you're backed into a corner.
[TAKEBAYASHI] But the comrade
we were most worried about
is doing fine.
[TERASAKA yells]
[TERASAKA grunting]
[YOSHIDA]
Is Terasaka for real with this?
It's a question
about probability.
He's usin' brute force;
essentially blowing through
each potential answer
as quickly as he can.
But, uh, aren't we supposed
to use a combination equation?
Meh...
Best strategy for a
lug-head like him,
if you stop and
think about it.
It's easy to take
too long fishing
for the most
efficient approach.
Sometimes it's better to come
out guns blazing before you
can second-guess yourself,
especially on this stuff.
[TERASAKA yells]
[KORO-SENSEI] Now when you
see a question like this,
don't be perplexed.
Simply use the tactics
I've shown you, like so.
Simplicity is your forte.
Think raw power
and go for broke!
Squish-squish!
Screw you, Octopus!
I may be a moron,
but I'm hella strong!
Ya gotta admire his fortitude,
even if he is an idiot.
Yeah.
[OKANO] Remember, guys:
we are the End Class!
We don't play it cool...
We play it quick and dirty.
[MAEHARA]
Heh.
[OKANO] Zero in on your
target's weakness!
[KIMURA]
If you know where to aim,
you can take it out in one shot!
You may not get
the right answer...
[SUGAYA] But if you take
the right approach...
[KIMURA] At the very
least you can get...
[MAEHARA]
Partial credit!
[SUGAYA]
Woo-hoo!
I think that did the trick!
No time for review, people!
On to the next one!
[ALL grunting]
[ALL yell]
Aw, crap...
Recurrence relations?
At the end?
[NAGISA] I thought this
was just an urban legend...
They put it on a
junior high exam?!
[SUGAYA]
Mayday! Mayday!
[OKANO]
Hold on! I need to reload-- Ah!
[NAGISA]
It's not working!
[MAEHARA]
Karma!
Oh, c'mon I showed
you guys last week.
You have to take it to
a particular solution.
[KORO-SENSEI] In addition
to their regular classes,
I had the students
tutor each other
on their strongest subjects.
One of the best ways to deepen
your own understanding
is to teach someone else.
It also fosters a strong
sense of teamwork.
The effect on Karma
was extraordinary.
It patched up the gaps
in his knowledge
and polished him to
a brilliant shine.
Sure, but that Asano kid is a
real overachiever, too, right?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Correct.
And in fact, since grooming
A-Class for the exams
is no longer his concern. The
boy's marshaled all his know-how
and cunning toward
sharpening his own blade.
A perfectly valid use of
one's strength, of course.
Though to be entirely honest,
not even I'm sure which
method is better.
Relax.
Just do your best, okay?
You're guaranteed to get
at least partial credit.
Don't worry.
Leave getting full credit to me.
[GAKUSHU]
Now, then...
[KARMA]
How shall I finish him off?