[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey-dokey, boys and girls!
The Second Term midterms
are only two weeks away!
The time has come
to surpass A-Class!
I want us going
into this red-hot!
Hotter than hades!
Hotter than the sun!
[MAEHARA]
That's too hot!
[NAGISA] Ever since we
sidestepped Asano's little trap
at the sports festival, E-Class
had been hunkering down
for the midterms.
We were stoked.
But at the same time,
the atmosphere was uneasy.
Only five months left until
the assassination deadline.
The clock was ticking.
We were impatient.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Payback time!
[ALL whooping]
What a rush!
[YOSHIDA]
Yeah!
[OKAJIMA]
Wha'd I tell ya?
Coolest shortcut ever!
[BOTH]
Yeah it is!
[ISOGAI]
Guys! Wait up!
Hey! Not outside of class!
Relax! It's fine!
After the pole-toppling match?
People'd be suspicious
if we didn't do this!
[NAGISA]
This is incredible!
We should always
take this route!
[BOTH gasping]
[MATSUKATA]
Hm? Uh!
[thud]
[groaning]
What was that noise?
Y' all right?
[gasps] Oh my word!
I'll call for help!
[siren wailing]
It seems the gentleman
has a hairline fracture
of the right femur.
Doctor says he should be on
his feet in about a week or so.
What complicates this is that
you kids are a state secret.
He'll likely settle
out of court,
but my men have to
negotiate a gag order.
[NAGISA]
I can't believe we--
[whoosh]
[KORO-SENSEI growling]
Koro-sensei.
It... It wasn't our fault.
The street was too narrow.
Yeah, and who'd think
an old man'd be
ridin' his bike
through there, y'know?
Exactly.
I mean, what we did was
reckless and everything, sure.
But we were doing it to, like,
sharpen our skills and whatnot.
We gotta unwind. We're
under a lot of pressure.
Savin' the world's a big deal--
[KORO-SENSEI] Will that be
reported as my bringing harm
to some of the students?
[KARASUMA]
I'll overlook it this once.
I knew the risk
when I introduced
a higher level of training.
I take full responsibility.
You clearly weren't
ready. This is on me.
Sir, we're...
[BOTH]
Sorry.
[STUDENTS]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Perhaps you've grown too strong
for your own good.
You were drunk on power.
You neglected to put yourselves
in the shoes of someone weaker.
That makes you no different
than your counterparts
on the main campus.
[NAGISA] It stung to be
called out like that,
but what could we
say in our defense?
We screwed up. It's
the least we deserved.
[ripping]
[KORO-SENSEI] We are now exactly
two weeks away from midterms.
Consider yourselves prohibited
from studying for them.
This isn't a punishment.
There are simply other, more
important things to study first.
I ought to have included them
in the syllabus earlier.
[KARASUMA] Please, accept
the offer, Mr. Matsukata.
[MATSUKATA]
No!
For all intents and purposes,
I'll be bedridden for
upwards of two weeks!
After what they pulled?
Standard restitution won't fly!
Oh, no! I'll need
something special.
Something with a bit of
groveling involved, I think--
What the hell?
What just happened?
Am I losing my damn mind
or did this room just become
a florist's all of a sudden?
[KORO-SENSEI] Please accept
my sincerest apologies!
[screams]
[KORO-SENSEI] I can't tell you
how contrite I am, good sir!
My would-be assassins and I have
caused you a world of trouble!
I beg your forgiveness!
[screaming]
[TEACHER] Attention,
children. I have news.
I'm afraid that Principal
Matsukata has been hurt,
and we won't be seeing
him for a little while.
[KIDS]
Aww...
Now, now. Don't
worry, he's fine.
And until he's back, these
young men and women
will here to lend us hand.
Isn't that nice?
[KIDS]
Yay!
[SAKURA]
Hmph.
[KIRARA]
Seriously?
Are you a witch?
Why do I have to watch
these freakin' zygotes
for something I didn't even do?
Worst job ever.
[KIRARA]
You're being eaten.
Hey, we're a team.
We all got a sticky slap.
He said for even one of us
to learn their lesson,
the whole class
has to be onboard.
I'm sorry, guys.
Aw, it's all right.
We got ourselves into this.
We should've had the sense to
know someone could get hurt.
Yeah, whatever.
As long as I get to
appoint myself supervisor.
Though with you clowns,
it's more appropriate
to call me ringmaster.
[MURAMATSU, YOSHIDA]
Hey!
Huh. I propose we can stealth
study for midterms at home.
And thank our lucky stars
we got off so light.
Two weeks unpaid work?
Small price to pay for
the old man's silence.
We should be grateful.
Takebayashi.
I can't take you seriously
when you're being pantsed
by six-year-olds.
[OKANO] Some of these
kids are kinda hyper.
[SAKURA] So, what do you insects
plan on doing for us now?
You descend on our habitat
like a swarm of locusts.
I figure the least you
can do is work off
some the oxygen you're
sucking up, you losers.
[ALL] And some of them
are just plain terrifying.
[BOY C] Uh-oh. Sis Sakura
is in a bad mood again.
[BOY A]
Yeah.
[BOY C] These guys aren't
gonna get massacred.
You think they know she's
been here for five years?
[BOY C] Or that she she's
spent the past two of 'em
rebelling against "The Man"?
They don't call Sis Sakura
the Elite Neet for nothin'.
Isn't she way too
old for this place?
I don't know, dude.
Don't judge.
Maybe she just
really likes it here.
The real question is
whether you troglodytes
have it in you to work.
--How 'bout an endurance test?
--[NAGISA] Hang on. Wait.
[NAGISA]
Be careful.
That section of the
floor is all wonky.
You're getting it fixed,
right? The building.
I mean, it does seem to be
getting sorta rickety.
If only we had the funds.
Our principal has a
soft spot for children
stuck on the waiting list
for primary school.
Takes them in at
rock bottom rates.
He can barely afford
the faculty he has.
Poor man works
himself to the bone.
All 28 of us are
here for two weeks.
I bet we could do a few things.
Yeah, a whole lotta things.
That's the spirit.
All right then, gang.
Let's divvy up the workload.
First, a strategy meeting.
[MAEHARA, KAEDE]
Yeah!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Please, Sir Karma,
you must stop!
I implore you not
to hurt anyone else!
Forgive me, Princess.
Honor compels me to
run the creature down.
As long as he lives there can
be no peace in the realm. Ha!
Quit going off book, damn it!
The script says no
physical contact.
You were gonna smack me
around either way, weren't ya?
Oh, wow. The fight
chorography is good.
No kidding!
And the girl's acting really
draw me into the story.
Knock it off!
To your rest!
[KIDS gasping]
[KAEDE] Suddenly, the
mage's magical chloroform
put the beast to
sleep, unharmed.
And, thanks to chemistry, they
all lived happily ever after.
[BOY D]
Sneaky!
[KAEDE]
That's our show, boys and girls!
What did you think?
[SUGAYA]
Kayano's fantastic with kids.
[SUGINO]
Yeah.
Girl's got a real gift
for reading the room.
Plus, she's their size.
So, what're we doing
with all this stuff again?
Oh, you'll see. Chiba
and Ritsu have blueprints.
[SUGAYA] Cool. Leave
the decorating to me.
[KIMURA, OKAJIMA, MAEHARA]
And drop.
That's awesome!
Do you wanna try?
Heck yeah!
Aw, she's so adorable!
Uh-oh. Is the poor
kitty cat lost?
You kids are wonderful.
Who'd have thought these
children would ever be tutored
by students from a prestigious
junior high school.
Don't expect much, ma'am.
Kunugigaoka might be great,
but our class is definitely
bottom of the barrel.
[NAGISA] Sharp as she is,
Sakura's falling behind.
Till she moves on
to primary school,
the girl's basically just
spinning her wheels.
'Kay, let's see.
How do I explain these
equations in a way
someone her age can understand?
Man, this whole teaching
thing's harder than it looks.
Oh come on! I don't
have all day! Ugh.
At this rate I'll be middle-aged
before Tokyo University
accepts me!
Hey, this takes time.
[NAGISA]
So, uh...
Why'd you drop out
of primary school?
If you don't mind me asking.
[SAKURA]
Huh?
Why do you think,
genius? Bullying!
They treated me like poop.
[SAKURA]
It doesn't make sense.
You'd think kids that age
would be sweet and innocent,
eyes filled with wonder.
Yeah, well the second they
learn how strong they are,
all they care about is picking
on the ones half their size.
[NAGISA]
That was a little on the nose.
[SAKURA] I know what you're
gonna say, so don't bother.
"It gets better. Stick it out,
otherwise the bullies win."
That's the same line
my parents feed me.
[SAKURA]
Whatever.
I mean look who I'm talking to.
You're weaker than I am.
You know how it is.
[NAGISA sighs]
[HINANO] Here, kitty,
kitty, kitty, kitty!
[BOTH]
Uh?
[CAT meowing]
[HINANO]
Oh dear.
I don't think she knows
how to get down.
Poor widdle thing
probably doesn't have
that much tree-climbing
experience.
Ya see what I mean?
The higher you go,
the more dangerous it is.
That's what courage gets you.
Thanks, but this gal prefers
to keep her feet planted
firmly on the ground.
Great, now we're dealing
with a cat in a tree.
I'll handle it.
C'mon, man. Like we
did in pole-toppling.
Sure, yeah!
I'm on catapult duty! Ha!
[NAGISA]
Look at it this way.
Let's pretend the tree
is primary school, right?
Where we're standing
is, well, this place.
We all start here, essentially.
And it's where our
strength comes from.
[KIDS]
Whoa!
We were looked down on, but
we never stopped looking up.
Even when the height made us
feel dizzy or insignificant,
or scared the crap out of us.
We learned how to climb by
taking it one rung at a time.
Who's a good, kitty?
Ow, my eye!
We reached the top,
but along the way we
forgot what it meant
to be scared of heights.
So every now and
then we lost our grip.
Learn to climb.
Start from where you are now.
Formulate a game plan.
When you're ready, go for it.
That's my advice.
A trade secret from one
late bloomer to another.
Nagisa.
[NAGISA] We learned a
lot in those two weeks.
And not the sort of stuff
they cover in school.
At least not when
you're a student.
Before we knew it,
time had flown by.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Again, sir,
I can't thank you enough
for letting us do this.
We greatly appreciate it.
[MATSUKATA grunts]
Anything to help young people
become more well-rounded,
I suppose.
How could a fellow
educator say no to that?
Well, anyway, let's hope
that ramshackle lean-to
hasn't collapsed under
the additional weight.
Hm? Uh?!
[FEMALE VOICES]
Before!
After!
What in god's name have
you done to my school?!
[KORO-SENSEI] The wood you
see here comes care of
the lush mountain
forest in which
E-Class's own facility sits.
This was once a cramped and
oh-so humble preschool building.
[KORO-SENSEI]
But what have we here?
An elegant and open,
multipurpose space.
How in the--? They did
this in only two weeks?
[KORO-SENSEI] Virtual mock-ups
guaranteed a sturdy design.
Robust pillars now
firmly buttress
the dilapidated main building.
We were inspired by
world architecture
and the Golden Ratio.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The second floor is divided into
two beautifully
functional rooms.
One a library, where the
children can read in comfort.
To be honest, it's
a very simple design.
We could only do so much.
But the shelves are packed.
We all scoured the neighborhood
for secondhand books.
I donated, too!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Adjacent to the library
is a posh indoor playground.
Careful placement of foam mats
and durable netting
ensure safety.
And, protected by a
weather-treated roof,
the equipment won't erode
from exposure to the elements.
[MATSUKATA]
I don't believe it.
Here. Come take a
look at the garage.
[MATSUKATA]
We have a garage now?
[MATSUKATA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Goodness gracious!
Our illustrious tech squad
has completely remodeled
the principal's bicycle,
whose front wheel got
banged up in the accident.
Once an ordinary conveyance,
it's now an ultra-safe,
high-load bearing
electric three-wheeler.
The rotating jungle gym is
linked to the battery charger.
Meaning that the bicycle runs
primarily on the kinetic energy
produced by the children
during recess.
[KORO-SENSEI] Meaning also,
the more the children play,
the more they help
their beloved principal
get from point A to point B.
Hooray for science.
This is too perfect!
You kids have gone
above and beyond!
It's actually a little creepy.
[KORO-SENSEI] Repurposed for
use with a handlebar bell,
the principal's old dentures
add a touch of nostalgia.
That's entirely too much
attention to detail!
Damn it, look.
You can spruce up and
spit-shine all you want,
but what my kids
need are mentors
who can speak
to their experience.
If you haven't gotten
through to them,
this was all just a whitewash.
[SAKURA]
Hey, Nagisa!
Ta-da! I came in second!
Wow! That's fantastic!
Great job, Sakura!
The trick you told me
to do really worked!
I snuck in for the math portion
of the test like a ninja.
I finished. I left. Poof.
Pretty cool, huh?
The bullies were too busy
with their own exams
to mess with you.
[SAKURA]
Mm.
I caught them by surprise.
The teacher was the only person
who knew I was coming.
We call that getting the
drop on your opponent.
It's how we do
things in E-Class,
and it's done wonders for us.
Unveil your best attack
before the enemy even
gets into position.
I'm so proud of you. Keep on
using those hit-and-run tactics.
When you're ready
for primary school,
you'll have a full arsenal.
[SAKURA]
Um, so...
[NAGISA]
Uh?
You'll, uh, teach me
some more tricks, then?
Absolutely!
[MAEHARA]
That is one scary dude.
[MEG] He's terrifying
because he has no idea
how terrifying he is.
You little ratfinks.
You've left me no room
to complain, damn it.
Oh! Welcome back,
principal. Look at this.
[MATSUKATA] Suppose it's time
to run along back class now.
I believe there's some
important work ahead of you.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KIDS]
See you later!
[NAGISA]
And with that,
our very special lesson
was at an end.
Still, though...
[NAGISA] The midterms
were the very next day.
[NAGISA]
It was a disaster.
The majority of E-Class got
booted out of the top spots.
[ALL sigh]
[ARAKI]
What a total letdown.
Oh well. Guess that first
time was just a fluke, huh?
[SEO] We didn't even need to
crush you at pole-toppling.
Aw, what's the matter, dorks?
Kitty cat got your tongue?
Grades are the end-all
be-all of this institution.
The bottom feeders have no right
to address the top echelon.
[KARMA]
No kidding?
Then by that logic I guess
you got nothin' to say to me.
[KORO-SENSEI] Despite
being forbidden to study,
one student remained undaunted
by the two-week handicap.
Of course, substantial traces
of prep work were clear
when I popped by the day
of Summer Festival.
One can't help but admire
the young man's initiative.
[sighs]
[KARMA]
I shouldn't get cocky.
Teach'll probably be all like,
"Nah, it doesn't count
'less you come in first."
Whoa, Karma.
Don't you people get it?
I'm the only one here you gave
it his all this time around.
Everybody else was
pulling their punches
to give you idiots a fair shot.
See, they were bein' nice
'cause we knew losing
would be worse for
you than for us.
Excuse me?
So, yeah. This was a freebie
and you only get one.
C'mon, guys.
[NAGISA] Ha. Thank you, Karma.
You just covered for us.
[ISOGAI] We're sorry for
the trouble, Mr. Karasuma.
It won't happen again.
No harm, no foul.
All in a day's work.
Did you learn your lesson?
[ALL gasp]
Did you kids take anything
away from this experience?
[STUDENTS]
Uh?
[NAGISA] That we're not
in this just for the money
or to bump up our grades.
We're in this to get stronger,
and to use that strength
for the greater good.
To help people.
Knowing how to kill gives us
the power to save the world.
Intelligence gives us the power
to change someone's life.
And we learned not to be
reckless with our strength.
From this point forward,
we'll be careful.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Failure and frustration
can be wellsprings for growth.
Something tells me my boys
and girls will be richer
for this experience.
From here on out, they'll apply
themselves more thoughtfully.
Now then,
time for some BBQ
with the foie gras
I purchased at a
French farmer's market.
Glad I could keep
this feast on the DL.
[chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[KORO-SENSEI] Wh-Where the
blazes did you come from?
Whoa. That was a serious drop
and I barely felt a thing.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh? Wh-What's going on?
I scarcely had time to breathe!
[ISOGAI] Sorry, sir.
We wanted you to see this.
[KARASUMA] Brand new equipment
from your pal, the government.
I told them not to tip their
hand, but they couldn't resist.
They felt it was important
that you see for yourself
how discreet they can be.
[KAEDE chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ooh.
Whatever you teach us,
we'll use it to kill you.
That's how Assassination
Classroom works.
But don't worry, sir,
you have our word.
We'll use what you
teach us for good.
See, as far as we're concerned,
our strength is for
protecting people.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Full marks for that answer.
When first I came to this class,
what bloodlust I
found was aimless,
and even then only a handful
of you possessed it.
There was negligible danger
of being assassinated,
but the atmosphere was stagnant.
Now however,
the whole campus is alive with
razor-sharp killer instinct.
[WOMAN]
I bet one of these days
you'll meet someone
just as important to you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Indeed.
At the moment, I seem to be
surrounded by several.