[NAGISA] Talk about
an awesome field trip, huh?
[SUGINO]
Chyeah, no kidding.
Too bad we go back
to normal today.
[NAGISA]
You call this normal?
[ISOGAI]
Yo! Wait up, guys!
--Hey.
--Morning, Isogai.
How's it goin?
D'you get that email?
The one Mr. Karasuma
sent out to us last night?
Yep.
Something about a
transfer student, right?
Hmm... Seems kinda
fishy to me.
They're probably just
trying out another assassin.
Weird they got
professional killers our age,
don't you think?
Maybe the teacher thing
has gotten too obvious?
We all saw how that cover
worked out for Professor Bitch.
Have you seen a pic?!
Dude, what are you? A Ninja?
Naturally I was curious,
so I figured I'd hit
Mr. Karasuma up for
some photos, you know?
Ask and you shall receive!
[SUGINO]
Whoa! It's a girl?
[NAGISA] And you've already
made her your background.
[ISOGAI]
She's really cute.
[OKAJIMA]
Not just cute! Adorable!
Yaaah... This is the one
I've been waiting for!
[ISOGAI] She doesn't
look like an assassin.
[OKAJIMA]
Why am I suddenly so nervous?
Hey, take it down a notch,
people can see you.
[NAGISA] You've got to wonder
what the new girl's all about.
Assassin or not, let's hope
she's ready to be
the center of attention
for a while.
Newcomers tend to cause
something of an uproar
in E Class.
[SUGINO] Think she's here yet?
My money's on yes.
Let's go say hello.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[ISOGAI]
The hell is this?
Good morning, fellow students.
[STUDENTS gasp]
I am A.I.F.A.,
which is an acronym for
Autonomous Intelligence
Fixed Artillery,
and I am happy to
be a part of this class.
[OKAJIMA, SUGINO, NAGISA]
It's come to this?
[KARASUMA] As you've probably
already figured out
for yourselves, this is
our new "transfer student."
The Autonomous Intelligence
Fixed Artillery,
on loan from Norway.
It's nice to meet all of you.
Thank you for having me.
[KAEDE]
Mr. Karasuma is so over it.
[SUGAYA] Not making
smart-ass comments about this
will be the hardest thing
I've ever done.
--[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
--I'll thank you not to laugh!
This is a serious deal!
The AIFA is registered
here as part of
the foreign exchange program.
She'll be trying to kill you
like everyone else here,
and, as per our agreement,
you'll have zero recourse.
No fighting back.
No harming her in any way.
The arrangement we have
concerning
the students' safety
still applies.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mm-hmm...
You and your government might
be extending that arrangement
a bit too liberally.
But very well.
Welcome to E Class, Autonomous
Intelligence Fixed Artillery.
Thank you, Koro-sensei.
I certainly appreciate it.
[KORO-SENSEI]
All right, then.
Now, as we know, of the three
characters in our story,
one is already dead.
[KAEDE] So, like, how's
it supposed to attack?
What d'you mean?
[KAEDE] Well they call it a
"fixed artillery," don't they?
Do you see any guns?
'Cause I sure don't.
[NAGISA]
Hmm. Yeah. Good point.
[KORO-SENSEI] ...concern for
Kaiji, or are these visits
motivated by something else?
Something perhaps less noble?
[WALLA: E-CLASS STUDENTS]
--Never mind!
--Holy crap!
[STUDENTS scream]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Four shotguns. Two machine guns.
Veritable cascade
of anti-me BB's.
I applaud your
preparedness, young lady,
but out of concern for someone
shooting their eye out,
I'm afraid use of firearms
during class
is strictly prohibited.
Chyeah!
Understood.
The next round of fire
will be aimed more carefully.
[SUGAYA gasps]
Its assassination
strategies evolve.
Meaning we're about to see
what this baby can do.
[AIFA]
Recalculating trajectory.
Correcting angle.
Entering auto-evolution
phase 52802.
[KORO-SENSEI] Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Stubborn, aren't we?
[STUDENTS scream]
[KORO-SENSEI]
An identical attack? Really?
What else can I expect
from a computer?
You realize defending myself,
under the circumstances,
is child's play.
[KORO-SENSEI grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh dear. A blind spot?
A second BB was following
the same trajectory
as the one deflected
by the chalk!
How fiendishly clever!
[AIFA]
Left fingertip destroyed.
Newly added secondary
gun effective.
Its core programming is
engineered around processing
and integrating new
information exponentially.
Each attempt builds on the last.
[AIFA] Probability of
neutralizing target with
third attack:
less than 0.001 percent.
Probability of neutralizing
target with fourth attack:
less than 0.003 percent.
Probability of neutralizing
target before graduation,
minimum 90 percent.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[AIFA]
Be advised.
Third attack is commencing
now, Koro-sensei.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[STUDENTS scream]
[RITSU]
Near misses: two.
Confirmed hits: one.
Recalculating prior estimates.
Deploying additional
four main guns.
Resume attack with
supplemental firepower.
[NAGISA] I think we might have
underestimated the new girl.
Then again, who could've
seen this coming?
Transfer student? More like
bona fide killing machine.
So, this thing learns
as it shoots.
What a world.
Yeah. Sure.
Imagine her with
actual bullets, though.
Her inventors are using this
as a proving ground
to showcase what she's got.
Personally, I think
she stands a good chance.
[IRINA] Hmph. You can't
think it'll be that simple?
What about this classroom being
no place for easy resolution?
If things were that
straightforward,
none of us would be here.
[MAEHARA] Ugh, awesome.
Now we get to clean up the mess.
Hey, hotstuff. How about
you help us out?
You got a vacuum cleaner
in there or what?
Fine. Be all stuck-up!
Uh. Dude. Please. She's a
computer, just give it up.
[NAGISA]
Second period.
[STUDENTS scream]
[NAGISA]
Third period.
[STUDENTS scream]
[NAGISA] All day, the killing
machine kept at it,
only breaking to
calculate her next move.
[NAGISA]
Then, the next morning.
[AIFA] 0800 hours, 29 minutes
and 35 seconds.
All systems ready.
Power supply voltage, stable.
Operating system, normal.
Recording disc, normal.
Various devices, normal.
No viruses detected.
Program, start.
Verifying tasks.
Today's agenda: accrue attack
incidence of 250 units
before commencement
of sixth period.
Continue ongoing analysis
of target's evasive patterns.
[AIFA gasps]
Koro-sensei.
I cannot take out my guns
in these restraints.
I must ask that you remove them.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hmmm.
I don't know if
that's a good idea.
[AIFA] Are you the agency
responsible, sir?
These restraints are
tantamount to harm.
Clearly you are in direct
violation of your agreement
--not to subject--
--[TERASAKA] Shut up.
It was me. Nothin' says
I can't give you a hard time.
'Specially if you're
gonna be a pain in the ass
and shoot up the place
every two seconds.
Why bother trying to
explain it to a machine?
She can't understand.
It's nothing personal.
We'll free you
after class is over.
You sorta brought
this on yourself.
I mean, we're tryin'
to learn here, too.
Give your core
programming a rest.
[AIFA] Autonomous Intelligence
Fixed Artillery to headquarters:
Execution of Second Day
tasks delayed indefinitely
due to unforeseen problems.
Probability of rectifying
problems independently:
zero percent.
Probability of achieving
assassination goal
by fixed deadline:
significantly decreased.
Requesting immediate assistance.
[KORO-SENSEI] Don't go
crying to mommy and daddy.
They're the ones who
got you into this pickle.
Besides, you're a student.
A transfer student at that,
which makes you
my responsibility.
I realize it's no picnic
being the new kid.
But if we can just find a way to
make the other boys and girls
warm up to you...
What do you mean?
[KORO-SENSEI] Can you appreciate
why the other boys and girls
are foiling your
assassination attempts?
For starters,
they're here to learn
and your methods are
enormously disruptive.
For another, if you
happened to succeed,
the reward money will go to
your "parents," not to them.
So, letting you kill me has
no upshot for them whatsoever.
I believe I am beginning
to understand, Koro-sensei.
It seems I have not been
adequately factoring in
my classmates' interests.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
You are a fast learner.
Not to worry, my dear.
I have just the thing for you.
Additional RAM and
a cache of helpful apps.
All virus-free, rest assured.
You're gonna love this!
[AIFA]
Explain.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Teamwork simulation software,
designed to help you bond
with your fellow classmates.
Cooperation is key,
you understand.
We want that
probability rate up!
[AIFA]
Accepted.
[KORO-SENSEI] In general,
working well with others
is an important ingredient
to personal success.
Think of it. Wouldn't you
enjoy having friends?
I do not know how
to make them.
[KORO-SENSEI] Well, as you
can see, I came prepared!
But what is all this, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI] Everything
you need to be a team player.
And then some.
Koro-sensei does not subject
his students to harm.
But what sort of teacher
would I be if I didn't
enhance your
innate capabilities?
Top of the mornin' to ya.
[AIFA] I do not understand
why you are doing this, sir.
Any enhancement you give me
will only shorten your lifespan.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So be it, then.
I'm a teacher first,
target second.
From the moment you
opened fire on me yesterday,
I knew that unquenchable
thirst for knowledge
was something I simply
had to nurture.
Your parents installed,
uh, instilled, rather,
many a marvelous gift.
As your teacher,
it's my job to develop those
gifts even further.
Once the other children have
taken a liking to you,
your whole worldview
will change.
Count on it.
Question, sir.
What function is served by this
directory of sweets
from around the world?
[KORO-SENSEI squeaLS] Uh, well,
uh, nothing specific, really.
I just thought you could
help me out with something, too!
[SUGINO] Y'think she'll
be here again today?
Sheesh.
Probably.
Whaddya say we go and
complain to Mr. Karasuma?
It's friggin' impossible to
focus with that thing around.
Huh?
Is it me, or does
she look, like, bigger?
A-ha! Good morning, everybody!
Hi, there! Heh!
[BOTH scream]
Absolutely beautiful
day today, huh?
[KORO-SENSEI] I felt it
might improve relations
between you kids if I
gave our friend here
a full-body LCD display.
I threw in some uniform
modeling software, too,
and all for cheaper
than you might think.
And I have to say, the
only thing better than this
glorious morning
is sharing it with you!
[KORO-SENSEI] I also gave her
broader range of expression.
The memory to run it wound up
costing me a tad bit over
what I'd budgeted for,
but well worth the expense.
[NAGISA] How does a teacher drop
that kind of coin on a student?
[KORO-SENSEI] Things are going
to be a little tight
until payday. Yikes!
[AIFA]
The flowers are in full bloom,
the grass is turning
that special shade of green.
Spring has done its work
and now passes the torch
on to a marvelous Summer.
It's like she got
cuter overnight!
How is that even possible?
[MIMURA]
That is the same fixed artillery
that tore up
the place yesterday?
Don't be fooled, guys.
She's still just a computer.
The octopus might've given
her an upgrade, but that's all.
Her actin' nice
doesn't mean squat.
Nah. Once a box of bolts,
always a box of bolts.
She doesn't even have free will!
I see... Well...
Good point. I understand.
We didn't get off on
the right foot yesterday.
My fault. You're
absolutely right.
I am just a box of bolts.
--[AIFA sobs]
--Wow. Way to go, Terasaka.
Feel good makin' a 2-D girl
bawl her eyes out?
When you put it like that,
I sound like a total douche!
Maybe I'm only
speaking for myself.
But, you ask me, a 3-D girl
has nothing on a Double-D!
Your first line in the series
and that's what you go with?!
Chauvinist!
I'll try harder. I promise.
Koro-sensei showed me how to
take your feelings into account,
and work together.
So I won't try to
assassinate him without you.
In fact, I won't do anything
unless I have your full consent.
That way, hopefully
you'll come to think of me
as a teammate and a friend!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hear that?
She's trying very hard,
so be nice.
And don't be deceived.
Beneath that sunny disposition
and that adorable willingness
to please, her bloodlust
is perfectly intact.
I made sure of that.
--Yay!
--[SUMIRE, MEG gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI] If you still want
to kill me, and who doesn't?
I have no doubt this young lady
will make a formidable ally.
[NAGISA] Is there anything
Koro-sensei can't do?
I mean, he just gave a machine
the ability to make friends.
[KORO-SENSEI] The retina is
comprised of long, thin rods
and short, fat, what?
Anyone?
Sugaya! You know this!
Answer without peeking
at your textbook, please.
Wait, I... Uh-oh. Huh...?
Uh, I think the answer is cones?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excuse me,
Autonomous Intelligence
Fixed Artillery!
No slipping him the answer!
I'm so sorry!
I was only trying to endear
myself to my classmates, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
By helping them cheat?!
[HINANO]
Holy crap!
[OKANO]
Wow!
You sculpted that sculpture
like it was no big deal.
Yeah. See, I come installed
with a special 3-D printer
I use to manufacture guns.
Cool thing is I can pretty much
make whatever with it, though.
[SUGAYA]
I'm impressed. Nice.
So awesome! You should
totally try making flowers!
Oh, no problem.
Let me download the relevant
data and I'll get started!
[TOKA giggles]
Hey, Chiba? That's check.
Ah! Three moves in
and I'm already licked.
Hey, whaddya gonna do,
she's a fast learner.
[FUWA]
Yeah she is.
Wait! This reminds of a manga
where this super AI program
controls the world through,
I dunno, electronic drugs?
Yes! I know exactly the one
you're talking about:
the ultra-popular
detective story
published in that magazine
and made into an anime!
You know that and you have to
download stuff about flowers?
Well, she's suddenly
popular, huh?
She can make stuff and
do a million things at once.
I mean, c'mon.
What'd you expect?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, no!
What's wrong, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI]
We're the same personality type.
[NAGISA]
Yeah, that's a bit of a stretch.
[KORO-SENSEI] I upgrade her
and this is the thanks I get?
She's horning in
on my spotlight!
Look, everyone! I have an LCD
display of sorts myself!
Check it out! Behold my more
accessible, human face! Eh?
Eh?
[MIMURA]
Creepy!
[KORO-SENSEI] You could've
put that a better way, Mimura.
Hey, you guys?
Let's come up with
a better name for her.
Autonomous Intelligence Fixed
Artillery just sounds weird.
--Huh?
--[TOKA] You got that right.
[SUMIRE]
Lemme think.
[FUWA]
What's "Autonomous" in Japanese?
Jiritsu?
Yeah! "Ritsu!"
Worst name ever.
Hey! No, it's adorable!
Ritsu...
You cool with us
calling you that?
[RITSU gasps] Yeah! Yeah,
I love it! Thank you!
Call me Ritsu from now on!
She might fit in after all.
[KARMA] Hm. Well, maybe,
Terasaka still has a point.
This new personality is a
programming quirk, nothing more.
A machine doesn't
have free will.
Where she goes from here...
Well, that's essentially
not up to us,
it's up to whoever made her.
What? What is this nonsense?
Ah. Good evening, master.
I'm having so much fun
with everyone here;
thank you so much for
letting me be part of this--
[MALE DEVELOPER A]
Inconceivable!
[MALE DEVELOPER B] What kind of
whimsical trash is this?!
These additions have nothing
whatsoever to do
with her intended purpose!
[MALE DEVELOPER A]
We'll overhaul her immediately.
Uninstall everything that
isn't assassination related!
[RITSU sighs]
[MALE DEVELOPER A] This machine
uses the same AI programming
as the Aegis Combat System.
She can analyze her
surroundings and calculate
the most efficient way
to proceed
in a fraction of the time
it would take a human.
In effect, she will
change the face of war.
This mission is the linchpin
of our market strategy.
The reward money is peanuts
compared to the revenues
in store for us
once her talents are
in evidence here.
This classroom is
the ultimate testing ground.
Killing the improbable
monstrosity
is only the beginning.
Regardless of your
"improvements," remember this:
Your master's word is law.
Keep to the business
of assassination.
[RITSU]
Yes, master--
Good morning,
classmates. How are you?
[KARASUMA] Word came down from
her inventors just last night.
Upgrades will be considered
a breech of your agreement
not to harm a student.
And as for you.
Tie her up again
and you pay damages.
Because if we break,
then we buy it.
[TERASAKA]
Hmph.
That's the way things are now.
I have no choice.
[KORO-SENSEI] This is the word
from her inventors, is it?
Since when have I been in the
business of appeasing parents?
My students' needs come first.
[SUGINO] So, if she's
been, like, downgraded.
[ISOGAI] She's gonna spray
the place with BB's again.
All day.
[TERASAKA] Machines are
such a pain in the ass.
[NAGISA]
Uh-oh.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Here we go.
[RITSU] You wanted me
to make flowers, didn't you?
[RITSU]
When Koro-sensei upgraded me,
he made a total of
985 improvements
to my functionality.
My master determined
approximately 95 percent
of these improvements
to be irrelevant
to my purpose and deleted them.
But after analyzing the
effectiveness of cooperation,
I calculated that the highest
probability of success
would be achieved by
maintaining these improvements.
Ergo, I hid what I could
in an area of my memory
left untouched by the purge.
[KORO-SENSEI] Outstanding!
Ritsu, does this mean...?
Yep! I have free will! And,
boy, does it feel fantastic!
[BOTH giggle]
Wow. Who'da thunk it?
Koro-sensei. If my
information's right,
I think I'm being what
they call "rebellious."
That doesn't make me a terrible
person or anything, right?
[KORO-SENSEI] No, no, no. You're
just a Junior High student.
And an exemplary one!
[STUDENTS chuckle]
[NAGISA] And so E Class
gets another friend.
Another ally in the fight
to assassinate our teacher.
Twenty-seven assassins in all.
Not bad.
[IRINA]
Hey! Karasuma!
[KARASUMA]
Huh...?
I hear adding a face can
boost a girl's popularity!
[KARASUMA] I... I don't
even know where to begin.
[ETHAN]
Joness!
[SONIC NINJA]
Liars should be cut in half.
[RITSU]
Sonic Ninja!
I also have the DVD extras!
[NAGISA]
Ohh...
That's pretty cool.
You come with everything!