[STUDENTS whimper]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
All right, people.
Let's get started, shall we?
Class Monitor,
if you would do the honors.
Right! Ready!
[NAGISA]
Aim!
Fire!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Oh. Oh, my.
Well, why don't I just call roll
while you children
wear yourselves out?
Isogai?
[ISOGAI]
Here.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
What's that?
I'm afraid I couldn't make it
out over all the gunfire.
[ISOGAI]
Here!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Okajima?
[OKAJIMA]
Here!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Okuda!
[OKUDA]
Here!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Kataoka?
[MEG]
Here!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Kayano?
[KAYANO]
Here!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Kanzaki!
[KANZAKI]
Here!
[NAGISA panting]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Excellent.
All present and accounted for.
No tardies! Congratulations!
[NAKAMURA]
He's fast.
[ISOGAI]
The whole class opened fire
and he doesn't
even have a scratch.
[NAGISA]
Yep.
We're assassins,
and our target...
...is our teacher.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
No luck today either, eh?
That's really too bad.
What's the lesson here?
Numbers are no substitute
for inventiveness, perhaps?
That any hack can point
a gun and pull a trigger?
Some of Column A,
some of Column B?
I get that you were
trying to cast the net
as widely as possible,
so to speak,
but the approach
lacked originality.
When the target clocks
at Mach Twenty,
an assassin has to
think outside the box.
[MAEHARA]
Ha. Right. Mach Twenty.
No freaking way did you dodge
that hail of bullets!
[SUGINO]
He's got a point.
I mean, these are
only BBs, right?
For all we know, you just stood
there and took 'em like a champ.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER sighs]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Collect the
ammunition and bring it here.
As was explained:
these are anti-me BB's.
Harmless to you, but--
[STUDENTS gasp, scream]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Able to split my cells
like a knife through warm tofu.
Developed by your government
for that express purpose.
Of course, after a few seconds,
I can regenerate good as new.
A luxury you won't have if you
accidentally shoot your eye out.
--[STUDENTS sigh]
--[OCTOPUS TEACHER] From now on,
no discharging guns
in the classroom.
Safety first.
And good luck killing me
before graduation.
You're going to need it.
Firearms and government issue
anti-me BB's away, please.
Time to get to work.
[NAGISA] Kunugigaoka
Junior High, class Three-E.
The Assassination classroom.
[NAGISA] The bell rings,
another day begins.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER laughs]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Okay,
here's a puzzler for you.
Isogai!
[ISOGAI]
Uh, sir?
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Which of these four tentacles
is the odd man out?
[ISOGAI]
Um, the blue one?
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Excellent!
"The boy who is standing"
employs "who" as a
relative pronoun.
--A relative pronoun...
--[KAEDE] Hey, Nagisa.
Check it out.
Crescent moon's up.
During the day.
Neat, huh?
[NAGISA]
How did this happen?
How did we get here?
I mean, as far as I know,
it all started with
two very big things
kicking off third year.
[NAGISA]
First, there was the moon.
One minute, it's fine,
the next, kaboom.
Permanent crescent.
Ahh... We interrupt our
currently scheduled program
for this breaking
news bulletin--
This just in.
A portion of the moon
has been vaporized.
Some sources estimate over 70%.
I repeat: according--
What does it mean?
Astronomers the world over are
struggling to figure out
just that.
[NAGISA] There was that,
and then there was him.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Hello! How are you?
So, I'm the one
who blew up the moon.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Next year,
I intend to do the same
to Planet Earth.
But never mind that now, I'm
gonna be your new teacher!
Isn't that exciting?!
[STUDENTS] There are so many
things wrong with this picture.
[NAGISA] It was a
strong first impression.
Uh, I'm Karasuma.
I'm from the
Ministry of Defense.
What, uh, what I'm
about to tell you
we in the business
call "classified."
[sighs]
Aw, hell. I'll just
come right out with it.
I'm gonna need you to kill this
thing for the sake of mankind.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[MIMURA]
Excuse me.
No offense, is this a joke?
'Cause if that's the alien
who blew up the moon--
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
A-bah-bah-bah-bah-bah!
I am an Earthling born and bred,
thank you very much!
[NAGISA]
Uh. Okay.
I'm not at liberty to discuss
the details at this juncture.
I'll just say he's
telling the truth.
His threat is all too real.
As of this coming March.
He will obliterate the Earth.
Apart from you, the only people
who know this are world leaders.
If word of this leaks out
to the public,
we'll have widespread
panic on our hands.
He must be terminated soon
and with extreme prejudice.
Which means that you
must become assassins.
Now, you'll notice
he's incredibly fast!
And for some reason,
he likes grooming eyebrows.
Immaculately!
[STUDENTS scream]
[KARASUMA] You're looking at
a being so powerful
he can obliterate over
half the moon in seconds.
So fast, he's been
clocked at Mach Twenty.
A world where
he's allowed to live
is a world waiting to be
destroyed, plain and simple.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] He makes it
all sound so grim, doesn't he?
Cheer up!
I've graciously made
your government an offer.
"Stop making fools of yourselves
trying to kill me," I said.
"And let me teach Class Three-E
at this illustrious
institution!"
[NAGISA]
Seriously?
[KARASUMA]
We didn't have much of a choice.
We have no idea
what his motives are,
but we agreed on the condition
that none of you students
would be harmed in any way.
[KARASUMA]
The advantage is twofold.
On the one hand,
we'll know his whereabouts
a good portion of every
weekday, which is something.
On the other, he'll be in
close range to thirty people
with the means and
incentive to kill him.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Nakamura!
I distinctly remember saying
no guns discharging
in the classroom!
[NAKAMURA]
I know...
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Back row, young lady.
Think about what you've done.
[NAKAMURA groans]
[NAGISA] Why would this "thing"
want to be our teacher?
And how are we going
to assassinate him
if the government can't?
Those're the questions we
should have asked at the start,
but I guess we got distracted.
[KARASUMA] Do the deed
and you get ten billion.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KARASUMA]
It's only fair.
Kill him, save the Earth.
If that doesn't deserve
a life on Easy Street,
what are we fighting for?
He doesn't think can do it.
Use that.
Green stripes indicate
he's feeling superior.
We have some experience with it.
[MAEHARA]
Freaky.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Truth be told, I'm not worried.
The military couldn't kill me,
why would anyone
assume students could?
After all, you don't
even have fighter jets!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Hard to keep tidy, fighter jets.
[MEG]
What's with the cleaning fetish?
[KARASUMA]
It's all on you.
Find the cracks in this
smug bastard's defenses
and exploit them.
The weapons you'll be provided
are harmless to humans
but extremely fatal to him.
And, it goes without saying,
we'll need to keep
this between us.
The clock is ticking.
Decide whether you'll
stand for our home
being blasted to space dust.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] That should
just about cover it, I think.
What do you say we hit the books
and make the final year
of your lives a productive one?
[NAGISA] So that's it.
We have a year to live.
If we can't find a way
to kill our teacher,
Earth is gonna be history.
[school bells chime]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Oh? That's lunchtime, everybody.
Excuse me while I pop over
to China for a quick bite.
You have my cell number,
any killers feeling
especially trigger-happy today
are welcome to hit me up.
[STUDENTS gasp, yell]
[NAKAMURA]
Okay, math...
If he's traveling
at Mach Twenty...
[NAGISA] It'll take ten
minutes tops to reach
his favorite take-out
place in Sichuan.
[MAEHARA]
So, just to be clear:
we've absolutely
ruled out missiles?
[ISOGAI]
Are you kidding?
Even if we had access
to that kind of hardware,
he can break the sound barrier.
[NAKAMURA]
While grading.
[ISOGAI] My homework even
came back with a doodle on it.
[NAKAMURA]
All things considered,
you have to admit
he's not doing a bad job.
[HINANO] I know, right?
He tutored me on algebra
and I killed it on
our pop quiz the next day!
Yeah. Kind of a shame.
We get our grades up just
in time for the world to end.
[OKAJIMA] Well, college
wasn't happening either way.
[NAGISA] Flying super-cephalopod
bent on world-destruction?
Check.
Impossible target?
But he might be the best damn
teacher any of us has ever had.
Forget that we're all
would-be assassins,
and that most people
probably see us as average,
garden variety third years.
At least on the surface.
Underneath it all, though.
Class Three-E has
always been different.
[TERASAKA]
Yo, Nagisa.
Look alive, little man.
Time to put our money where
our mouth is and get this done.
[NAGISA]
Mm...
[TERASAKA] So we know the
octopus's face changes color
depending on what mood he's in.
Have you been keeping track
like I asked? Gimme the specs.
You got it.
I guess for starters, green
stripes mean he feels cocky.
So that's something.
When we give a wrong answer,
his face goes dark purple.
When we answer correctly,
bright red.
What's interesting is every day
after lunch, without fail--
[TERASAKA]
Blah blah, whatever!
We got more 'n enough.
When his guard's down,
that's when we make our move.
Well, at least you do.
Yeah. About that, I--
Don't start!
We've been over this!
Worried about your transcript?!
Wake up, dude! We're Three-E!
Everyone expects us to be
thugs and murderers anyway!
You know what the E
stands for, right?
End of the line.
Think they shuttle us up this
mountain every day for the view?
Sorry to burst your bubble, man,
but society don't want us.
When do nobodies
like us have a shot
at the kind of
cash at stake here?!
This is our one-way ticket
out of the boonies!
No guts, no glory.
Let this be
your moment to shine.
--Huh...?
--Man up.
Go make a name
for yourself, huh?
[TERASAKA laughs
Best of luck.
Try not to blow it...
[BOY STUDENT A]
You hear about Nagisa?
They're chuckin' him to E-Class.
[GIRL STUDENT A] Heh. Shocking.
What else were they gonna do?
[BOY STUDENT B] That's one
less name in my contacts,
I'll tell you that.
[BOY STUDENT C]
Yeah. How messed up is it that
we even know
someone like him?
[gasps]
[NAGISA grunts]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Hello there! I'm back!
Okay, hi, sir. So, what...
what's with the missile?
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
A souvenir from a strike force
that tried to bring me down
over the Sea of Japan.
[NAGISA] Must be lonely spending
your life in the crosshairs.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Quite the opposite, actually!
Reminds me of how amazing I am!
[NAGISA gasps]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Now, then.
Inside for fifth period, please.
Sure...
[NAGISA]
There's no denying it.
He is amazing.
Confident. Capable.
Powerful enough to make
people stand up and take notice.
Even if they are
trying to kill him.
Everything I'm not.
Everything I'll never be,
no matter how hard I try,
or how many chances I'm given.
Because of you, I received
the worst teacher's evaluation
of my career,
you un-teachable brat.
Far as I'm concerned, this
campus can't eject you
fast enough.
[NAGISA] I can do this.
I have an advantage.
I'm as invisible to him
as I am to everyone else.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Okie-dokie!
Your assignment this afternoon
is to compose a short poem.
The final line should read
"was tentacles all along"
[STUDENTS]
What? Huh?
[KANZAKI]
Excuse me, sir. Really?
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Really!
When you've completed
the assignment,
kindly bring it forward.
You will be graded on
creativity, grammar,
and overall beauty
of expression.
Here's an example:
"Not the storm of garden's
snow of flowers moving on,
but sprouting there instead
was tentacles all along."
Yeah, because that
makes a whole lot of sense.
Sheesh.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] You may
go home once you're finished.
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--What? But, sir!
"Was tentacles all along?"
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Should get
those li'l synapses sparking
and the imagination slithering!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER sputters]
[MAEHARA] Could you
please knock that off?!
Um, sir? Question!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Huh? Of course!
Fire away, Kayano!
Do we always have to
call you sir?
You haven't given us your name
and I think we need one.
I mean, it'd be kinda awkward
if we don't call you
anything, right?
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Ah. Well, now...
Oversight.
Yeah, a little bit.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Hmmm...
Trouble is, I don't have
the sort of name
you just give to people.
Why not pick one for me?
[MAEHARA]
What could go wrong?
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Just focus on meter and syntax.
M'kay.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
I'll take a short break
while you take up your pens.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Ah!
Seems the muse favors Nagisa.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[NAGISA] Every day after lunch,
without fail, he gets sleepy.
I can tell he checks out
when his face turns pink.
Kayano's question threw
him off, he seems distracted.
All signs point to this
being the right moment.
[NAGISA]
Prep-school flunkies know
how to slip between the cracks.
It's what we do.
Parents and teachers are
always yapping at us
to "apply ourselves."
[NAGISA]
Apply ourselves.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] What did I say
about thinking outside the box?
[NAGISA]
All right, then.
Here goes nothing.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER gasps]
[TERASAKA]
Hmph!
[STUDENTS scream]
Ha! Yeah!
We did it!
--[KAEDE] Nagisa!
--[YOSHIDA] Yeah!
We're gonna be billionaires!
Sayonara!
--You jerks!
--What the hell have you done?!
Hah! Never saw a suicide
bomber comin', did ya?
[KAEDE]
Terasaka!
What'd did you make Nagisa do?!
What? I'm sorry,
you have a better idea?
I gave him a
modified toy grenade
filled with those stupid BB's.
And a spoonful or two
of gunpowder
so they'd scatter at a
high enough speed.
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--Don't worry,
it wasn't enough
to kill anybody.
I'll pitch in
on his medical bills.
Huh...?
Whoa. He doesn't even
have a mark on him.
And, what the hell
is this membrane?
Did the body, like--?
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
It's not a body, it's a husk.
I shed my skin once a month.
I wrapped it around
your classmate
to protect him from the blast.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] I'm gonna go
out on a limb here
and assume you
didn't see this coming.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Terasaka.
Yoshida. Muramatsu.
[STUDENTS whimper]
[NAGISA] Okay, that's a face
we haven't seen before.
[whimpering continues]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER growls]
[NAGISA]
Pitch black must mean pissed.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
This was your doing. Wasn't it?!
Who...? Us...?
It was all Nagisa!
[STUDENTS scream]
[TERASAKA]
Huh--?!
[STUDENTS scream]
[gasping]
[TERASAKA]
The nameplate off my house!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Here's the deal, kiddos.
The agreement I have
with your government
forbids me from harming you.
But there's a catch.
If you pull another
irresponsible stunt
like that again....
There's nothing that says
I can't harm someone else.
Family... Friends...
Everyone in the world except
for you, if I feel like it.
[STUDENTS whimper]
[NAGISA] Suddenly it's clear
how hard this is going to be.
We can't run, we can't hide.
Slipping between the cracks
isn't an option.
--[NAGISA] The only way out...
--[OCTOPUS TEACHER laughs]
--...is to kill him.
[TERASAKA]
Go on! Threaten us!
I ain't afraid of no squid!
Where do you get off
blowing up the moon?
We got rights, you know!
Call us irresponsible!
We're just defending ourselves!
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Of course. I know that.
I'm not calling you
irresponsible
for trying to kill me.
No, no, no.
As a matter of fact, Nagisa here
gets full marks for technique.
His composure was
simply outstanding.
However!
None of you cared
if he was injured.
Not even Nagisa
himself, it seems.
Students with that attitude
aren't fit to
assassinate anyone.
You must believe yourself
worthy of your target.
That means taking pride in
what you do, in yourselves,
and each other.
All of you are more than
the sum of your parts.
[NAGISA]
Chewed out at Mach Twenty,
reassured by a tentacle wag.
It's a bizarre education.
But one I think is
starting to grow on me.
I guess, when you spend your
whole life being invisible,
well, it's something to
feel like you're being seen.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Heh.
[FEMALE RESEARCHER A]
If you....
If you could sacrifice a
little bit of your time.
Give the children the tools
they need to succeed.
Such wonderful tentacles.
With hands like these,
you could reach them.
I know it in my heart.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER] Here's a
puzzler for you, Nagisa.
Given that I have
no intention of being killed.
Though, of course,
I have every intention
of enjoying our time together
before the planet
goes kerplooie.
What, exactly, are
you going to do about it?
[gasps]
[NAGISA] That's the
big question, isn't it?
It's not like we have
a lot of experience
figuring out how to
save the world.
I have a feeling, though.
One way or another...
...we're gonna be fast learners.
I think you'll find out
I can do plenty, sir.
Just you wait and see.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER laughs]
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
That's the spirit!
No one leaves
until I'm vanquished!
[STUDENTS groan]
[NAKAMURA]
Way to go, Nagisa.
[MAEHARA]
This is totally balls!
[NAGISA]
Yep. We're assassins.
Our target...
...is our teacher.
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Wipe it clean...
[SUGINO]
Man, I don't wanna be a killer.
[MAEHARA]
Ugh. We are so screwed.
[OKAJIMA]
We still don't know his name.
How do you say
"un-killable" in Japanese?
[NAGISA]
Huh?
Koro-sen-nai?
[gasps]
Koro-sen-say!
[NAGISA
"Koro Sensei?"
[OCTOPUS TEACHER]
Huh?
[NAGISA]
That feels right.
Just us and Koro-sensei.
Here in our
Assassination Classroom.