[KORO-SENSEI] A mere one tenth
of a gram of antimatter
puts out as much energy
as an atomic blast.
By splicing the
particle acceleration cycle
of antimatter into
the lifecycle of a cell,
Yanagisawa's research enabled
rapid regeneration
of organic compounds.
His subject, the legendary
assassin known as
the Reaper, underwent
a daily battery of tests.
Coursing through
the subject's body,
antimatter energy appropriated
the tissues to create tough,
flexible limbs, possessed
of an astonishing dexterity.
Yanagisawa dubbed
these "tentacles,"
and reinforced the restraining
table as a precaution,
leaving Aguri alone
to monitor his creation.
She, in turn, was not
unaware of the danger.
She understood that
the Reaper knew neither
his real name nor
the day he was born.
That his easy smile
and gift for small talk
were simply part of his
wheelhouse as a killer.
And he understood her.
He could see there was no love
between her and her fiancé,
the brutal Yanagisawa.
He knew that her little sister
was an acclaimed actress.
A year had passed since
this unlikely pair's meeting
and somewhere along the way,
they'd become something
not unlike old friends.
Oh! I almost forgot!
You haven't seen the fancy
new top I'm wearing today yet!
You never learn, huh?
Your taste in clothes sets
women back by ten years.
Ta-dah!
It's a tube top with
a cute oni pattern!
A little tight, sure.
But crazy stylish!
[chuckles]
[AGURI] Uh... Um... It's
too out there, isn't it?
--Sorry.
--No, no!
--It looked super cute
--I just, uh!
on the mannequin.
[KORO-SENSEI] Are the
experiments doing this to me?
[giggles] Those tentacles do a
good job of keeping you honest.
I don't think they
choose their shape at random.
It's just possible they
reflect how you'd prefer
to see yourself.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What do you mean?
Imagine what you'd be now
if you hadn't been born
where you were.
You'd still be smart, slightly
perverted, a little bit goofy,
not to mention
remarkably stubborn.
But your smile would
be open and honest,
not just a means to an end.
[AGURI]
Hey, Akari.
Turns out my schedule's open
tonight. Wanna grab dinner?
[KAEDE]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why do you sound like you're
on cloud nine all of a sudden?
Who's the new man in your life?
[gasps] U-Um!
What're you talking about?!
You know I'm engaged!
Oh, don't give me that line.
Drop the jerkface
and find someone
who treats you like a person.
--[AGURI] Don't go there.
--Anyway, I'm down.
If you tell me all about this
guy who's caught your fancy.
[AGURI]
So is that a yes?
[KAEDE]
You bet. Your treat.
[AGURI]
Ugh...
A present for me?
Yeah. You keep saying
your neck is cold, so...
This ought to keep you warm,
and more importantly,
it's fashionable!
Thanks...?
[AGURI]
Oh. You're not a fan.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No, no, I...
I just-- I mean, why a
present out of the blue?
Because as of today,
it's been a year since we met.
And since you don't know
when you were born,
why not treat our "anniversary"
like your birthday?
You listen to me babble
on about my personal life
all the time, and give
me great advice.
So please, as a friend,
let me give you
a proper birthday.
Well, all right, then.
Okay, it's settled.
'Cept, of course, I'm not really
sure how to give you this.
Guess I forgot to
factor in the glass.
Awkward.
Yanagisawa's hounding me
to quit my teaching job
and work here full-time.
[AGURI]
Maybe I should...
I mean, the latest
crop of students...
They're so, I dunno, unique.
I'm not sure I can reach 'em.
I just... I'm too green.
Too... whatever.
Still, though.
This may sound cheesy, but,
they're a good group of kids.
It's students like them that
make we want to teach
in the first place!
I can't quit.
I can't give up on other people.
They need a teacher,
someone who believes in them.
This hurts so much.
I wish I could hold you...
You've been my rock
through all this.
If I had your strength,
I could...
I could get through
one more year.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Before he realized it,
his smile was no longer
just a means to an end.
Hang in there, okay?
You've got what it takes.
Thanks...
[KORO-SENSEI] The first time
they knew one another's touch,
was three hours before
the moon exploded.
[SHIRO]
The moon?!
[MALE RESEARCHER A] Yes, sir!
Seventy percent destroyed!
An anti-matter discharge from
a lab rat on the lunar surface!
So, then... cell division,
exceeded natural limits?
Right! Calculate how
long we have until
our human subject reaches
the same breaking point!
Yes, sir!
[alarm sounding]
[MALE RESEARCHER A] Okay.
The algorithm projects
March 13th of next year.
The day the Reaper will die and
take the entire world with him.
[AGURI gasps]
[MALE RESEARCHER]
What should we do, sir?!
[SHIRO]
Isn't it obvious?
We put him down like a dog.
It's really only a matter
of stopping his heart.
You! Notify the
Americans immediately!
[MALE RESEARCHER B]
Done!
So I'm doomed to die
a horrible death. So what?
It's not like
I don't have it coming?
You can't give up
without trying!
--There has to be a way--
--[KORO-SENSEI] That said,
it'd be a shame to waste
this power in the meantime.
It's been fun, Aguri.
Goodbye.
[gasps]
I think it's about time to go.
Sooner than expected, maybe.
But I know I'm more than
equal to the challenge.
I've been here long enough.
No, wait! This isn't you!
You're not the person you were!
[KORO-SENSEI]
You gonna stop me?
Yes!
Oh, really? With what?
Those little arms?
That stunning intellect?
[AGURI gasps]
Unless your abilities
surpass mine, sweetheart,
you don't have a prayer
of stopping me anymore
than you do saving me.
Frankly, you're not
even worth the trouble
of taking as a hostage.
So unless you want a
pointless death, leave. Now.
[AGURI]
It's Yukimura. Unlock door One.
I need out.
[KORO-SENSEI] All right.
Time for a test drive.
Let's reap the fruits of torture
and see what I'm capable of!
What's wrong with
the security system?!
I don't know!
It's not responding!
The artillery panels are stuck
in the closed position!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Much obliged, Yanagisawa.
This new body--it's
affectively invincible.
Then, of course, I did give you
quite a bit to work with.
[SHIRO] The bastard's been
playing us from the beginning!
[AGURI]
Kotaro, please!
You have to do something
right now! Help him!
[SHIRO]
You stupid bitch!
Fawning on every man you meet!
Is this the thanks I get
for taking you in?!
Is it?!
Who do you think you are?!
Dammit! Don't just
stand there like idiots!
Go on! Arrest him!
[SHIRO] Don't push
your luck, guinea pig.
And don't assume we're strictly
in this for the science.
Fire!
[KORO-SENSEI] If you're trying
to hit a major artery...
[yelling]
...a grain of sand
will do the trick.
I could have slaughtered the
likes of you whenever I pleased.
[SHIRO giggles]
Tentacle mines!
A byproduct of
antimatter organisms.
All one need do
is attach sensors.
And presto!
A supersonic projectile!
Grafted onto human beings,
they become the ultimate
killing machine!
[KORO-SENSEI] You're gonna
need more than this.
I don't die that easily!
[laughs]
K-Kill him!
Block him in and fire at will!
[laughs]
[grunting]
Drop the acrylic shield!
[screams]
[KORO-SENSEI snarling]
[cackles]
[AGURI groans]
It doesn't matter...
I'll die in a year either way.
Whether it's here
or somewhere else.
Heh. If I take the Earth
with me, so much the better.
[grunting]
No, stop!
[AGURI]
Don't leave!
If you do,
there's no turning back!
You're... You're
better than this!
[KORO-SENSEI]
She had seen everything.
And despite it all,
she was hopeful.
I... I hadn't expected
her to react as she did.
This was something
completely new.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Aguri!
[AGURI] Okay...
That was really stupid...
Sh-Should've paid closer
attention to where I was going.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
Why? Why did you...?
[AGURI]
I-I had a sneaking suspicion
yelling wouldn't be
enough to stop you.
[KORO-SENSEI] If I'd been there
a fraction of second quicker,
I could've saved her.
If I'd thought about using these
tentacles for something
other than killing...
Why? There was more
than enough time...
Why didn't I...?
Why couldn't I just...?
Why must it always be death
and destruction?!
Why? Why...?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, God, Aguri.
I've killed you...
[giggles] Don't be so dramatic.
This wasn't your fault.
It's on me.
No one made me come after you.
I knew the risk, accepted it,
and chose my priorities.
That's just how important
to me you are, silly.
I bet one of these days,
you'll meet someone
just as important to you.
[KORO-SENSEI] There is no one
as important as you.
Sorry...
You should've been
the one to kill me.
[AGURI rasps]
[AGURI] Listen...
You have a year left...
If you could sacrifice a
little bit of your time,
give the children
the tools to succeed...
In a way, they're like you.
Wandering in the dark,
waiting for someone
to turn on the light.
Someone who can
take them as they are.
Warts and all.
[AGURI]
Such wonderful tentacles...
With hands like these...
you could reach them...
I know it... in my heart...
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm sorry...
Then he really understood.
Her many faults had been
part of her charm.
[KORO-SENSEI] In the time I have
left, I will be a teacher.
I will take up
the torch in your honor.
Take the children as they are.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No matter what...
I will never turn
my back on them.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The tentacles spoke to me.
Asked what I wanted to be.
"To be weak," I said.
"To be flawed. Vulnerable.
To perceive weakness in others.
Not to exploit, but protect.
To be a guide.
To be a teacher."
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sometimes I'll be wrong.
Sometimes my old self will
bubble up to the surface.
But... I'll give it my all.
I'll honor Aguri's memory.
Carry on her work
the best way I know how.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's my story, boys and girls.
The person who taught me
how to be a teacher
was none other
than Aguri Yukimura.
She taught me to
truly look at people.
To respect everyone as an equal,
not define human beings
by their weakness.
She was wonderful. Through her,
I found my purpose in life.
I evaluated my experience,
collected all the knowledge
I could, and prepared to
pick up where she left off.
I vowed to use
my abilities to the fullest.
To pass the gift of
personal growth on to you.
The question was: how?
How best to reach
her cherished E Class?
I racked my brain,
day and night.
And suddenly it came to me.
An entirely new kind
of learning environment.
The Assassination Classroom.
[NAGISA] It'd been nine months
since Koro-sensei appeared.
We'd all grown
by leaps and bounds.
Whatever his past,
he was the best teacher
we could've asked for.
Hearing his story,
we understood the reasons
he'd decided to
become our teacher.
Vividly, in living color, our
minds flooded with memories
of the past year.
The scary times.
The infuriating times.
The happy times.
The fun times.
Yeah, especially those.
[NAGISA] Gradually, the nature
of what we'd been asked to do
dawned on us. Our mission
became all too real.
[NAGISA] Before it's all over,
we have to kill our teacher.
[IRINA]
Hey. Karasuma.
Do you know what it
means to kill?
To actually end someone's life?
[NAGISA]
The end was nigh.
Slated for March 13th.
Ironically enough,
the same day as our graduation
from Kunugigaoka.
We've rung in the New Year.
Today is January sixth.
And the number of us
hatching assassination plots
over the Winter Break?
Was precisely zero.
[NAGISA] So, how's it goin',
Kaya-- Sorry, Miss Yukimura.
You can call Kayano.
After all this time,
the name's grown on me.
Sorry about your Winter Break.
I don't imagine the holidays
were all that much fun.
Well, hey, at least I'll
make it back for the new term.
What about you?
D'you make use of the time off?
Not so much.
Assassination plans were just
hard to think about.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
It's all my fault, really.
Now that I've been
told the truth,
there's at least some sense
of closure about Aguri.
But knowing where
Koro-sensei comes from
doesn't make this any easier.
[NAGISA]
You can't blame yourself.
The truth was gonna
come out one way or another.
We've all been in denial.
None of us wanted to face
what this was about.
I mean it's been blast, right?
And who's had time to think
about were it was leading us?
Everyone spent the
break wondering how
we're gonna face
what's left of the year.
You're right: It's all fun and
games until things get real.
Oh! I almost forgot.
I owe you an apology.
Sorry about the kiss. Honest!
It was... the only thing
I could think to do
in the heat of the moment.
You mad at me?
Are you kidding? That kiss
happened to save my life!
I'm totally in your debt now!
Ugh, what a relief! I was sure
you were through with me!
[KAEDE]
You worry too much.
BFFs for life!
We should probably head out.
I'm certain she needs her rest.
Right, right. Let's go.
Bye, Kayano.
[OKUDA]
See you in a couple days.
[SUGINO]
Later.
[KAEDE]
For sure.
[giggles]
What's the matter? You good?
Just think about it.
She's been on
the outside looking in.
But now it genuinely feels
like she's part of the team.
[KAEDE groans]
[screams]
[KAEDE]
I can't do this!
It was... It's like I was being
brainwashed or something!
This is my life from now on!
What the hell
am I supposed to do?!
I was the top assassin
in our class, hands down.
Those tentacles gave me an edge.
Speed, firepower, the works.
Nobody had a better chance
of killing Koro-sensei!
And yet...
I was shot through the heart.
Taken down by a kiss.
I'm defeated, bumped out
of the top spot.
Nagisa flung me
back down to Earth.
[KAEDE] So now I play
the part of his friend?
I guess so...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey-dokey, class!
Third term is upon us!
I want everyone to
play hard and kill hard!
[KARASUMA]
You can't be surprised.
You knew the kids'd
be like this.
The atmosphere's changed.
They feel the gravity of
what needs to be done.
Question is: What does
that do to your sense
of being their teacher?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Very little, actually.
If I wasn't prepared
to adapt as needs demanded,
I wouldn't have become
a teacher in the first place.
[IRINA] An assassin
can't afford to be reckless.
We don't kill out of greed, we
don't kill out of desperation.
We don't let ourselves
become animals.
[HINANO]
Professor Bitch...
Our feelings are always
the first target.
Only when they're cold and
buried do we train our sights
on the second.
That's the cost of doing
business, and it's high.
Take my word for it.
Whatever you kids decide,
think it through first.
Feelings are difficult to kill,
but they're a lot
harder to resurrect.
[TERASAKA]
Okay.
Ain't really like you to call us
all together like this, Nagisa.
What's the deal?
There's something I wanted
to talk to you about.
[SUMIRE]
We're listening.
I'm not even sure
it's possible...
...but instead of
killing Koro-sensei,
I think we should
try to save him.