So he's holding
the kids hostage.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Indeed.
I suspect he's using them as a
means of luring me to my death.
[REAPER]
Aw, shucks.
Well that certainly throws
a monkey wrench in my plan.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Mr. Karasuma and Koro-sensei!
But I though he was in Brazil
for that big soccer game?
So be it. Plan 16.
[IRINA] Hmph. This is
my moment to shine.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Wh-what's this?
[KARASUMA]
The room's going down!
Huh? Irina!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't worry, my dear. Stay calm.
[KARASUMA]
I'm guessing this is your show?
[REAPER]
You've heard of the Reaper, yes?
That would be me.
[KARASUMA]
Lovro has mentioned you before.
[REAPER] Precisely why I
left the old fool alive.
See, when clearing the playing
field of competitors,
it helps if my reputation
precedes me.
Now, be a sport and lower
that gun, won't you?
Or shall I ventilate
your friend?
[KARASUMA] How is he
obscuring his presence?
[REAPER]
Heh.
Her neck's been fitted
with explosives.
Same goes for the children.
I give the high sign,
they detonate.
[KORO-SENSEI] You suppose if
my students are threatened,
I'll agree to die quietly.
Is that it?
Well, I am curious.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No one else is around.
So, if I'm mindful of his gun...
--[gunshot]
--[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Why?
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
[KORO-SENSEI] My tentacles!
He's fast enough to see them?!
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[STUDENTS chattering]
That was disappointingly quick.
Didn't even get to
liquidate a hostage.
Oh, well. Let's go say
a fond farewell.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Miss Irina.
[KAEDE]
Koro-sensei?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh. Hello, class.
I trust you're all unhurt?
[KANZAKI exhales]
[MAEHARA] No offense, sir, but
I can't believe he caught you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heh. The bars are forged
of anti-Me material, I see.
Tricky stuff to work
around, to be sure.
But you'll be thrilled to know
my body has at last overcome it!
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--Wait, are you serious?!
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
Behold, boys and girls,
my top-secret weapon!
The tongue!
[KORO-SENSEI] Coated by
protective digestive juices,
I'll have the bars worn down
to nothing in two days.
[STUDENTS]
We don't have that kind of time!
[REAPER]
Excuse me...
[ALL gasp]
Not to interrupt, but if you
want their neck braces
to explode, by all
means keep licking.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What?! Seriously?!
[REAPER]
Okay. Let's get on with it.
This room...?
'S about to be flooded.
[ALL gasp]
[REAPER]
We are in a drainage canal.
When I send the signal to
the control room above,
water will come gushing in
at 200 P.S.I. per second.
And these bars will essentially
become a giant noodle press.
[STUDENTS whimper]
Hold on!
You're not gonna do that
with the kids in there?
Of course I am.
It's too late to wait.
[KARASUMA growls]
Irina!
You knew this, would
happen, didn't you?!
I'm sorry.
Results are the only
priority here.
You wanted professionalism.
[KARASUMA grunts]
I realize my method
seems a bit harsh.
Would you prefer it if I let the
best chance of saving the world
slip through our fingers?
[KARASUMA] Sir.
What if a situation comes
up where killing him
means sacrificing the children?
Do we have a specific
policy on that?
Uh, let's see here. Take it
on a case-by-case basis.
Odds are it'll come down
to that at some point
before this is all over, so,
I... I'm certain you'll be
able make the right call
on our behalf.
[KARASUMA]
Here we are.
And in effect, it's my call.
Save the kids,
or save the world.
[KARASUMA] Here's the
government's official stance.
[REAPER]
Hm?
Saving the world isn't worth
the lives of 27 children.
If these kids are no more than
so much collateral damage,
I'm going to shut you down.
[STUDENTS]
You tell him, Mr. K!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Wow. He's so cool!
[KARASUMA]
FYI, Irina.
Huh?
A true professional gives a
damn about the bigger picture.
[REAPER] If I spend much more
time dealing with this nuisance,
my plan will fall apart.
Very well.
--[IRINA] Huh?
--[KARASUMA growls] Like hell!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mr. Karasuma!
Turn on your transceiver!
Moron. Him and his ethics.
Karasuma may stand
apart from the herd,
but the Reaper goes further.
Exhibit A: he trapped
the Octopus.
Please, Professor Bitch.
--[beeping]
--[IRINA] Hm?
[REAPER]
Irina, I need you.
I've set a booby trap.
While Karasuma's
trying to disarm it,
shoot him in the back.
[IRINA]
Understood.
[KARASUMA] Something's
not right about this door.
Probably a trap. I don't
have time for this.
I'll open it and
take a chance.
That do the trick?
Well, at the very least
it slowed him down.
Huh. Little more "umph"
to that than I expected.
[REAPER] You have an excellent
nose for this sort of work.
Clearly I underestimated you.
[KARASUMA] This place is like
a trade fair for booby traps.
I'm impressed.
[REAPER]
Ah, the more skills you pick up,
the more you want to use.
It's second nature
for an assassin
to revel in his bag of tricks.
[REAPER]
Mind your aim, Irina.
[IRINA]
Oh, don't worry.
My next shot'll definitely land.
You're going to die.
You know it.
[IRINA] Believe me,
I'm more than prepared.
I don't expect you
to understand that,
but some people can relate.
The Reaper and I are cut
from the same cloth.
[REAPER]
She's right.
Do you know what I was before
I was called to this work?
A scared kid living moment
to moment in a warzone
where every second, every
breath promised to be my last.
A place that taught me you
can only rely on three things.
Skill, money, and death.
Irina and I know what it is
to be nurtured on
blood and darkness.
[explosion]
[IRINA gasps]
Oh, yeah.
And what it means to be a pawn.
[REAPER]
Wow. You're alive.
Guess I should've known, huh?
Shame you're not in a
position to chase me.
Full disclosure?
I only enlisted your
associate as a decoy.
[gasps]
[KARASUMA]
Irina.
[REAPER]
Aw, well.
See you at the grand finale.
[KARASUMA]
No!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mister Karasuma!
Come in, Karasuma!
Are you okay?!
[KARASUMA]
Uh?
What's wrong?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, thank goodness!
I finally got through!
We heard an explosion!
Are you hurt?
[KARASUMA]
I'm all right,
but I'm afraid Irina's
trapped under the rubble.
[ALL gasp]
[KARASUMA] I don't have
time to dig her out.
The Reaper's getting away.
[HINANO]
Wait!
You have to do something,
you can't just leave her!
[KARASUMA]
Kurahashi...
Look, the woman
took her chances
when she partnered
with that psychopath.
Being a pro means
assuming a level of risk.
That's part of the job.
What does that have
to do with being pro?!
I know I'm only
a kid, but still.
Poor Professor Bitch!
She's barely even 21!
[HINANO] And childhood was
a total nightmare for her.
If life's a puzzle,
Miss Irina didn't
get all the pieces.
Who can say what she'd be
now if she had, y'know?
Please, sir.
Don't leave her behind.
I'm begging you.
[KARASUMA exhales]
[TOKA] You forgive us
when we screw up, right?
What's the difference with her?
[OLGA]
The village has been wiped out.
This one escaped, killing a
militia member in the process.
What do you think, my dear?
[LOVRO grunts]
[LOVRO]
Good eyes.
[gasps]
[LOVRO]
You have one decision, child.
Follow our bloodstained path
into life of an assassin,
and the horrors you've witnessed
so far will become routine.
You're free to seek
peace, of course.
But you'll be hounded by
nightmares all your life.
Only by embracing them
can the horrors be tamed.
[LOVRO] A cruel choice
for a child to make.
We will find refugee camp.
Hm?
There's no turning back.
[IRINA]
There you have it.
All my life I waded through
a cold sea of blood.
Death by betrayal
is a fitting end.
[IRINA]
I'm just glad it's all over.
If I'd held out much longer,
I might've remembered
what the sun felt like.
[KARASUMA grunting]
[IRINA gasps]
Well don't just
lie there, damn it.
I can't hold this much longer.
[IRINA gasps]
[REAPER]
Uh... What in the...?
They've all escaped?
[REAPER]
No matter.
Killing a few ought
to rein 'em in a bit.
[beeping]
[REAPER]
They took them off?!
Oh, they're good.
[growls]
[ITONA]
Those collars were crap.
All his RC can do is
detonate and unlock.
And if it'd been up to me,
I'd have made it
so the bombs go off
when the person tries
to get out of 'em.
It's just bad design.
[TERASAKA growling]
This really sucks.
[MIMURA] I'm impressed by
the design for these outfits,
though! They're so lightweight!
Good thing the security
camera has a blind spot.
He couldn't see us
makin' the camouflage.
Excellent job on
the shading, Sugaya.
[SUGAYA]
Hey, no prob.
My paint worked
great on this fabric.
Do I have an eye for
color-matching or what?
[MEG]
Fantastic.
The RC Creeper Squad
is never gonna let us
hear the end of this.
[MAEHARA] So...
What about Koro-sensei?
[MIMURA] He comes with his
own built-in camouflage.
[NAKAMURA]
Meaning he's essentially
buck-naked right now.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Now I'm ruined for marriage.
[MIMURA]
Stop blushing! He'll see!
[KARASUMA] Your left arm's
probably fractured.
[IRINA]
Mm.
Anywhere else you feel
pain or discomfort?
[IRINA coughs]
Huh? Hey, you're bleeding.
I'm fine.
Seeing you shirtless just has me
all hot 'n bothered, that's all.
I was worried there might
be some head trauma.
It's good to know this
is status quo for you.
Hm?
[IRINA]
Huh?
[KARASUMA]
He's back.
The kids figured he would be.
[KARASUMA]
Listen to me.
E-Class is a far cry from
the world you grew up in.
But...
What the hell, I'll just
come right out and say it.
O-Our world really needs you.
[IRINA]
Huh?
[REAPER]
Irina?
Where's Karasuma?
[IRINA]
No idea.
He was already gone
when I came to.
Pretty underhanded stunt,
by the way.
Did you have to try
and kill me, too?
Sorry, couldn't be helped.
My hands were tied.
"Can't make an omelet,"
and all that.
There may be honor
among thieves,
but assassins traffic
in deception.
What do I care?
Who am I to talk?
I'm just a bitch who switches
from one man to another.
[REAPER]
Mm?
You...
You're out of your mind!
[KARASUMA]
Y'know, I've been wondering.
Is this Reaper guy all he's
cracked up to be, or what?
[REAPER groaning]
[STUDENTS gasps]
[KAEDE]
What was that splash just now?
[REAPER gasps]
[KARASUMA]
Don't get me wrong.
Your skills are on point.
You just don't have
any endgame strategy.
Huh?
[REAPER] You've certainly
dressed me down.
[KARASUMA]
What the...?
[REAPER] Surprised?
Don't be. After all,
having no face makes it a whole
lot easier customize disguises.
Heh.
Yours will make a delightfully
rugged addition to my wardrobe!
[KARASUMA grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[NAKAMURA]
What's going on down there?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Um, er.
The Reaper has a knife!
No, wait! It's a wire!
He tried to strangle
Mr. Karasuma, oh, wow!
Karasuma parries and
does the... thing!
A-And, the Reaper stops him
but then Karasuma comes and,
oh, wow, somehow this is so wow!
What a stupendous fight!
We can't understand
what you're saying!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Stupendous!
Explain it so we can visualize!
[KARASUMA] I shouldn't have
pulled him into close-quarters
combat. Should've figured
he was hiding something.
Can't let this drag
out any longer.
[REAPER]
Ah, ha, ha.
I feel I should tell you,
Mr. Karasuma.
I might've overstated the tragic
circumstances of my childhood.
As a matter of fact I might've
made the entire thing up.
[KARASUMA]
You bastard.
When I was just a boy, an
assassin killed my father.
[KARASUMA grunts]
[REAPER] I wasn't particularly
torn up about it.
However, seeing the way his
killer moved, so swift, so sure,
it did give me something
to think about.
I said to myself:
what a beautiful skill!
I was captivated.
In that moment I knew:
Assassination is high art!
And the culmination
of that art?
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
[REAPER]
Let me show you.
[KARASUMA groans]
[REAPER]
The Reaper's hidden scythe.
A simple ten-caliber.
Nothing fancy,
but its miniscule bullets pass
easily through muscle and bone
to pierce the aorta.
Every heartbeat widens the hole
just a tiny, little bit, until.
Well, I'm sure you get the idea.
A fine composite art,
you'll agree.
That's the province of a Reaper.
[REAPER]
What?
This is...
--[KARASUMA grunts]
--[REAPER groans]
[REAPER chokes]
[KARASUMA] Thought
there'd be a good opening
if I timed it just right.
Nice to see the Reaper
has the same weak spots
as everybody else.
His tentacle?! Seriously?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I can slip at least one
through without injury
if I'm careful.
[REAPER] You faked me out
with tomato juice?
[KARASUMA] Sorry, friend.
You screwed up.
Messing with my students and
my colleague was a bad idea.
Wait!
Who else could conceivably
kill him if not me?
You'd be surprised
what a classroom full of
motivated kids can accomplish.
[REAPER groans]
[KARASUMA]
I think it's about time for you
to quit the killing game.
But hey, with all those skills,
they'll love you at the
unemployment office.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KARASUMA] The man had skills,
make no mistake.
But he just put too much stock
in 'em.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The man who set him on this path
was a first-rate fool.
His talents might've
served him just as well
on the straight and narrow.
I suppose it all boils down
to the world we know.
How it shapes the value
we put on life.
[NAGISA grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes. Well said.
Wouldn't you agree, Miss Irina?
[IRINA]
Uh... H-Ha...
[OKANO, MAEHARA]
Uh...
[MAEHARA]
Where you think you're goin'?
[STUDENTS yelling]
[IRINA screams]
[IRINA growls]
Go on and do your worst!
Think I'm not ready?
You li'l punk bastards are one
rung below animals anyway!
The boys pent-up,
the girls all insanely jealous!
Now's your chance to set
all those emotions off
like sexual fireworks!
Do you ever listen to
what you're saying?
Just shut up and come back to
school tomorrow like always.
No more takin' off
for days at a time.
And besides, you never
finished that story.
Conning Arabian
royalty, remember?
You had the region
on the brink of war.
If you don't come back,
you can kiss your copy of that
French manga you lent me goodbye
"Boys Over Flowers?"
Okay, just to be clear:
you do realize
I was going to kill you all?
[TAKEBAYASHI]
I don't see the problem.
A fair amount of treachery
is to be expected.
These things come with the
territory, do they not?
[IRINA]
Ah...
[NAKAMURA] I mean, c'mon, if we
can't handle a foul-tempered,
backstabbing bitch,
we really wouldn't have
a lot of room to say
we're cut out to be assassins.
[KARASUMA]
They're right, y'know.
Huh?
--[STUDENTS gasp]
--[KORO-SENSEI] Ah-ha!
[IRINA gasps]
[KARASUMA]
For you.
And before you ask,
nobody put me up to this.
Consider it taken from a
vanquished enemy in your honor.
Happy Birthday.
Sorry if I'm a little late.
[IRINA] He just shoves it in
my face like a barbarian!
And it's not even
a proper bouquet!
Un-friggin'-believable!
I should give the man
a piece of my mind!
Yeah, I'll tell him off!
It's lovely.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[FUWA] I do believe we have
some potential, guys.
[HINANO] No fair, I already
called dibs on him.
[TOKA] Oh, sweetheart.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mr. Karasuma?
A word before this situation
takes a turn for the racy?
Trust me, it won't.
What do you want?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Today was almost tragic.
I don't want the children
embroiled in something
like this again.
I must insist on an environment
where they can kill safely,
immune to the intrigues of
madmen like the Reaper.
Right there with ya.
[ONAGA] "Should any student
become collateral damage
in the course of an
assassination plot,
the bounty will be
null and void."
Uh. Uh...
Safe to say you've taken a
liking to these children,
Mr. Karasuma?
They have the right to a
reasonable expectation
of safety, don't you think, sir?
[ONAGA]
Fine. Condition accepted.
In any event, we, uh...
We're no longer seeking out
freelance help in these matters.
Too dangerous.
The time's come for
us to move forward
with the final
assassination project.
[KARASUMA]
When you get right down to it,
I have no clue where
this class is headed.
[KARASUMA exhales]
[KARASUMA]
How's your arm?
[IRINA]
It's all right.
[KARASUMA]
Either way,
this world of ours...
is a good place to be.