Keep eyes on the target.
Right. Don't let
yourself be distracted.
If you can't predict his moves,
you can't effectively counter
his evasive maneuvers.
[KARASUMA] Not too shabby
for four months of training.
Every day these kids
show more promise.
Take Isogai and
Maehara, for example.
Catlike reflexes.
When they work together, often
as not, their blades hit home.
Then there's Karma.
At first blush, all
sarcasm and laziness,
but behind that facade lurks
the instinct of a killer.
[KARASUMA]
And the girls.
Okano's gymnastics background
makes her moves hard to predict.
Meg easily has the
reach and momentum
of her male counterparts.
These are the standout,
would-be assassins of the group.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't forget Koro-sensei.
The ideal teacher.
A man of grit and character whom
none have the heart to kill.
This is my interior
monologue, damn it.
No one wants your two cents.
[KARASUMA]
Truth be told,
the other students may
have a long way to go,
but they've come a lot
further than I dared hope.
[NAGISA grunts, yelps]
[BOTH gasp]
[NAGISA]
Ugh.
Ouch.
[gasps] Sorry!
That block was a
little over the top.
Ah. I'm good, no worries.
Eyes on the target.
You gotta see stuff
like that comin'.
[NAGISA]
Yeah...
[KARASUMA]
Nagisa Shiota.
What the--? Did I just have a
momentary lapse of sanity?
[KORO-SENSEI grunts]
Man, I'm having no luck
hitting that guy.
[OKAJIMA] There's, like, zero
chinks in Mr. Karasuma's armor.
'Scuse me, sir?
We were wondering if you'd like
to grab a bite to eat with us.
Sorry, no. I'd love to,
but there's still a lot of
work that needs to get done.
[HINANO]
Oh.
[MIMURA] Zero chinks
in his personal life, too.
[OKANO]
He's definitely a man
who prefers to keep
his distance.
It's like there's a wall
of ice between him and us.
Yeah, don't get me wrong,
He's super cool and
everything, I mean...
I just, I don't know. You think
it's only 'cause he has to be?
[TAKAOKA]
Hey, hey, Karasuma!
[KARASUMA]
Takaoka?
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[HINANO]
Another new teacher?
[TAKAOKA
Yo! Name's Akira Takaoka
and I'm here to give
your gym teacher a hand.
Pleased to meet 'cha, gang!
So, whaddya say?
Ready to have fun?
[MIMURA]
Whoa! Is that?
[KAEDE]
It's cake!
[FUWA]
Handmade éclairs from Le Hermes!
Um, these look sorta
pricy, sir. Are you sure?
Yeah! Chow down, kiddos!
I didn't break the bank
so we could stare at
these babies all day!
You really know your way around
brand-name sweets, don't 'cha?
Nice.
Trust me. When it comes to
the good stuff, it's love.
[SUGAYA]
Built like a truck and adorable.
So, you're gonna take over P.E.
to help Mr. Karasuma
get caught up?
Yep! Those are my marchin'
orders from the brass at HQ.
Poor guy needs some
time to himself--
[KORO-SENSEI]
Cake.
Ah! And this fella
must be Koro-sensei.
Please, help yourself.
Heh. Don't wanna die
on an empty stomach.
[TAKAOKA laughing]
You know, sir, for
bein' colleagues,
you and Mr. Karasuma
are night and day.
He's nice to us and all,
but you're like the
neighborhood dad.
[TAKAOKA laughing]
"Dad." I like me
the sound of that!
Life's too short not
to spend it with people
ya think of as family,
am I right, gang?
[TAKAOKA, STUDENTS laughing]
[TAKAOKA]
All right, everybody here?
Now, things are gonna
be tougher than usual,
but stick it out like
the champs I know you are
and we're talkin' more sweets!
For us, or are you really
just saving them for yourself?
Nope, nope. Don't wanna
ruin this girlish figure.
[STUDENTS laughing]
How you kosher with this idiot?
If he was a toupee, a chinstrap
couldn't make him look phonier.
Even Karma can tell,
and he's not here today.
Look, he and I go back
to the Airborne Brigade.
We're not best
friends or anything,
but based on the information
I have, he's a great teacher.
[IRINA]
Hmm.
[KARASUMA]
Young people respond to him.
He speaks their language.
That's what you
want in an educator.
[KARASUMA] I think maybe
I've been going about this
the wrong way.
My approach was to draw
a line, stay professional,
but taking on the role of father
figure might be more effective.
Huh?
[KARASUMA gasps]
[TAKAOKA]
Okay, then!
Along with your new
training regimen comes
a new schedule!
[STUDENTS]
Huh? What?
[MAEHARA]
What? No way!
[FUWA]
We have ten periods now?
[NAGISA]
We train till 9:00 P.M.?
That's the idea,
little grasshoppers!
Don't be glum!
Think of the payoff!
This curriculum will
turn you into lean,
mean killing' machines!
You're gonna love it!
[MAEHARA]
Wait. Hold up, hold up.
This is ridiculous!
First off, this is school. We
gotta think about grades, too.
I mean, c'mon!
We can't go by this.
When are we supposed to study--?
[MAEHARA grunts]
[coughs]
Rule number one.
We don't do "can't."
Rule number two. We're
a family, and I'm the dad.
Show me a family where
the dad ain't in charge
and I'll show you
a family in crisis.
If this is too much
for you, sit it out.
I'll have my people back
at HQ send in replacements
for the whole class.
That said, I'd much rather
see you stick it out.
A father loves each of his
children unconditionally.
The thought of losing even
one of 'em breaks his heart.
We're gonna save
the world, kids,
and we're gonna do
it as a family.
[MIMURA, KANZAKI gasp]
[TAKAOKA] There are two
essential ingredients needed
to earn loyalty
of your students.
Affection and fear.
Well? You're gonna do everything
father tells you to, eh?
Uh. I--
[SUGINO]
Uh.
Actually, sir, to
tell you the truth.
I'm not much for P.E.
If I have to do it, I prefer
Mr. Karasuma's class.
[KANZAKI yelps]
[SUGINO]
Uh! Kanzaki!
Looks like we're having a
little communications gaff.
The only answer here is "yes."
If anybody else needs a dose
of good old fashioned
nonverbal reinforcement,
Daddy Dearest will
be happy to oblige.
[KARASUMA]
Stop it!
[TAKAOKA]
Hm?
Hey, did he twist your neck?
Try moving your
head side to side.
I'll be okay.
What about you?
Eh. I'll survive.
See? We're fine! Don't go
gettin' your boxers in a wad.
I'm not gonna go full
throttle on my beloved fam!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Correct.
Except they're not your
"fam." They're my students.
[STUDENTS]
Koro-sensei!
[KORO SENSEI] Whatever you've
been filling their heads with
while my back was
turned, it stops now.
Ha. Sorry, big guy.
This isn't your class.
You teach your subjects,
I'll teach mine.
In Phys Ed, I call the shots.
Nothing I've done falls outside
acceptable corporal punishment.
I gotta train these
kids to kill you.
That doesn't leave
me a lotta time.
I don't have the luxury
of goin' easy on 'em.
What, are you gonna attack me?
Over a dispute about
educational philosophy?
'Cause that's what this is,
you just don't care
for the way I teach.
[KORO-SENSEI] The man will crush
those children, body and spirit.
And he's right, and
I don't care for it,
but civility dictates I let
him teach as he sees fit.
That's why I'm counting on you.
You're on par with
this fellow, are ya not?
I need you to shut him down.
[KARASUMA]
Me? That's rich.
[TAKAOKA] Bet this really
grinds your gears, Karasuma.
Me stealin' these kids
out from under you.
You were always top
dog of our old brigade,
never gave a damn
about what I could do.
And yet, here I am
throwin' a monkey wrench
into your shot at promotion.
Let half of these snot-nosed
punks be pulverized.
If I can shape the other half
into octopus-killin' warriors,
it'll be me reapin' the glory
when the deed is done.
You'll be lickin' my boots
till the day they
put you out to pasture.
[SUGAYA]
This is seriously not funny.
[OKAJIMA] 300 squats?
We're gonna freakin' die!
Mr. Karasuma, please.
[TAKAOKA]
Watch it.
[gasps]
Mr. Karasuma ain't part
of our family, doll-face.
Someone needs a lesson.
Disrespecting daddy
makes him very angry!
[HINANO screams]
[KARASUMA]
That's enough.
If you hurt these kids, then
you'll have to answer to me.
Ah! There it is. I was wonderin'
when you were gonna throw
your chips in, old buddy. Heh.
[TAKAOKA] Waitin' to
make this interesting.
What's the big deal?
Who are you to criticize
how I choose to teach?
If this is something you an'
me need to settle like men,
then I'm up for the challenge.
Just remember,
we're teachers first.
Here's what I propose.
Cherry pick your star pupils
out of the students you've
trained by your methods.
Set 'em on me, and if their
knife so much as grazes my aura,
I'll concede that the way you
train is superior to mine.
No fuss. No back pedaling.
I'll pack it in and leave.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[TAKAOKA]
We won't be using these, though.
No, sir, we won't.
[STUDENTS gasp]
When the object is to
kill a human being,
you can't rely on toys.
So we'll be using
the real McCoy.
[KARASUMA]
He wants to use an actual knife?
This is ridiculous!
These kids aren't prepared to
take down a real human being,
and you know it!
Don't get all concerned
citizen on me,
they ain't gotta kill
nothin', just come close.
And I'll do you a solid by
defending myself barehanded.
[TAKAOKA] This little
trick works beautifully
in the big leagues, too.
Take a fresh-faced recruit
wielding a blade
for the first time,
pummel the poor bastard within
an inch of his life, unarmed,
and bingo! Instant
Alpha Dog status.
What're you waiting for?
Pick yourself a champion.
Or save us the headache
and agree to let me run
this show from now on.
[KARASUMA] Wish I could
say I was sure about this.
Are his methods
as bad as all that?
Maybe his
take-no-prisoners policy
is what saving
the world calls for.
[KARASUMA] I'm not sure
of anything anymore.
Still, look at 'em.
How could I put one of
these kids on the spot?
Do I even have a star pupil?
[KARASUMA]
Nagisa. You're up.
[SUGINO] What?
Wait, are you kidding?
In my eyes, we're all
fellow soldiers on a mission
to save the Earth
from destruction.
Whatever our differences
are, we share that goal.
The least you kids deserve
for being put in this situation
is my respect.
I may not be much
of a father figure,
but I appreciate your dilemma.
So if you don't
feel comfortable,
you don't have to
take up the knife.
Our duty as teachers is
to prepare you for life,
not force you into it
kicking and screaming.
[NAGISA] This man always
looks me in the eyes.
My own family can't even do
that. But him? No problem.
Man. There must be so much
he's not allowed to tell us.
And I can't imagine
why he's choosing me.
[NAGISA]
But...
[NAGISA] If he sees fit
to hand me the knife,
I'll trust his
decision and take it.
Either way, Takaoka
is out of control.
Somebody has to do something.
I'm your guy.
Oh, come on. This twig?
Eyes must be goin'
in your old age.
What would possess that
dumb bastard to pick him?
This is gonna be
a train wreck.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Patience. You'll see.
You think Nagisa will
get anywhere near him?
I don't think so. Guy's a pro.
Hell, how would you do
with a real knife?
[KAEDE]
Oh, Nagisa.
Ready when you are.
[TAKAOKA]
This is gonna be fun.
Time to school these kids in
the art of real humiliation.
Dodge. Taunt. Beat.
Wash, rinse, repeat.
[KARASUMA] It's important you
understand this is real to him.
He intends to make
an example out of you.
Treat this like any
other assassination.
You don't have to be
stronger than your target.
Just get one good strike
in and the job is done.
That's it. One.
[TAKAOKA]
It's dawning on him.
Stakes are pretty high when
the knife in your hand is real.
He's thinking, "Wait a second,
this is for keepsies.
I can't take the life
of another human being."
There's nothin' sweeter than the
sight of a rookie turning pale
at the thought
of his first kill.
[NAGISA] Okay, this is bound
to be a little different
than what I'm used to,
so I need to stay focused.
Just remember
Mr. Karasuma's advice.
One strike. I just
need one strike.
[NAGISA]
I just need to kill him.
So I'll give him a smile.
Walk towards him calmly.
Totally nonchalant. Like
I'm on the way to school.
[NAGISA] And before he knows
what's up, this gets real.
That's right.
You're about to die.
No one keeps it together
when they realize that.
Even Koro-sensei
gets thrown off.
And you're nothing
compared to him.
Once you lose your balance,
all it takes is a little tug.
Here, let me help
you down. There we go.
You can block from
the front. No problem.
But when it's an attack
from behind? Good luck.
Looks like I win.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KARASUMA]
What the hell?
Not something you see every day.
Son of a bitch. The talent
this kid's got in unreal.
The way he strolls
up to the target,
hiding his intent
until the last second.
Springing on them like a python.
That explains the chill
I got from him earlier.
This goes beyond
the instincts of a killer.
Nagisa isn't a normal boy.
He's a natural-born assassin.
But should I nurture a gift
like his, or shut it down?
Oh, wait a second.
Was I s'posed to use
the back of my knife?
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'll take that, thank you.
Game, set, and
match, Mr. Karasuma.
[KARASUMA grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Outrageous!
Giving one of my
students a real knife!
Have you lost your marbles?
He could have been
hurt, or worse!
[NAGISA chuckles]
[KARASUMA] Pretty sure you're
quick enough on your feet
to have kept that from
happening. Still, though...
[STUDENTS chatting]
Easy, guys. Let's not make
a big deal out of it, okay?
I just did what Mr. Karasuma
told me to, that's all.
Ow! What was that for?
[MAEHARA]
Sorry, uh...
I needed to make
sure that was you.
Sincerely, though.
You're awesome!
That whole ordeal
was a total rush!
[NAKAMURA] That smile on your
face right before you got him...
[KORO-SENSEI]
If ever a man unsure of himself
right up the moment
of truth, it's you.
Think so, huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mh-hm.
--[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
--[thud]
[BOTH]
Hm?
You ungrateful punks!
You think it's fun shaming
your father figure, huh?
Having the time of your lives
pretending you've won?!
Hope it was worth it
'cause daddy's about rip you
apart. Mind, body, and soul!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh-uh-uh.
[NAGISA] Not gonna lie, if we
went for a round two, I'd lose.
But I'll tell you something.
Whatever you do, you're
not the boss of us.
Mr. Karasuma is
our P.E. teacher.
That's all there is to it.
When you try to be our dad,
it just makes us
feel like children.
Mr. Karasuma may come
off as all business,
but he treats us as equals.
He's approachable, he's cool,
and he's got nothing to prove.
Thanks for trying,
but he's the Class Dad.
Am I the Class Mom?
[KORO-SENSEI]
To teach is also
to confront such answers
head on. Moreover,
to do so by drawing from the
well of their confidence in us.
A student confidently
answers a question
you yourself were troubled by.
And that's only the beginning.
[KORO-SENSEI]
To teach is also
to confront such answers
head on. Moreover,
to do by drawing from the well
of their confidence in us.
[yelling]
[KARASUMA] Sorry if my
colleague's a bit too big
for his britches.
He's not in a position
to threaten you.
Don't give him
another thought.
I'll negotiate with my superiors
to put things back
the way they were.
[STUDENTS]
Mr. Karasuma!
[TAKAOKA groaning]
It's gonna take more than
that to be done with me!
You'll get this job
over my dead body--!
[ASANO]
That won't be unnecessary.
[KARASUMA]
Principal Asano.
[ASANO] I trust you'll forgive
the intrusion, everyone.
I came to see our
new hire in action.
And it must be said,
your methods are nothing
short of a travesty.
Granted, fear is
the engine of education,
but a teacher able to instill
fear only through violence
is nothing but a brute.
And I do not employ brutes.
[TAKAOKA]
But I was only trying to--
[ASANO]
Your walking papers.
The Ministry of Defensive
does not call the shots here
and I intend to
keep it that way.
This is my school
and my school alone.
Remember that.
Damn it. Damn it. Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
[TAKAOKA crying]
The man got handed
a pink slip?
Does that mean
Mr. Karasuma's back
to being our gym teacher again?
[STUDENTS cheering, laughing]
[KORO-SENSEI] I see the
principal's confident as ever
in his methods.
[KARASUMA]
That makes one of us at least.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eh?
[KARASUMA] What if Nagisa said
he wanted to be an assassin
when he grew up?
Could you lead him there
with a clear conscience?
[KARASUMA] I don't think
he realizes it yet,
but he's got what it takes.
[KORO-SENSEI] That's certainly a
tricky one, I'll give you that.
Alas, such dilemma's
come with the territory.
Every teacher
secretly frets over
whether the path he sets his
students on is the right one.
But he points the way to the
best future he can see for them.
Questions of right and wrong
are often open-ended.
We ask them, but the students
must live their own answer.
The pleasure of
seeing them do so
is what makes this
job exhilarating!
[KARASUMA]
Hm.
[NAKAMURA]
Mr. Karasuma, sir?
We were wondering,
since we kind of got your
job back for you and all,
maybe we've got something in the
way of a li'l thank you coming?
Yeah. Mr. Takaoka
would've given us
a buncha sweets
for being so good.
Well now, I'm not much
of a connoisseur.
--I guess you could buy your--
--[IRINA] Yoink!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[IRINA]
Sucker!
[KORO-SENSEI] Uh, surely
I deserve some thanks, too?
[OKANO]
Ha. Oh yeah? For doing what?
[SUGAYA] You've pretty much been
on the sidelines the whole time.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Au contraire, boys and girls!
I was scrutinizing your plight
in thoughtful silence
in hopes of demonstrating
to Mr. Karasuma...
[HINANO]
Whatever. Let's go, Class Dad!
We can show you all the
best places to buy...
[KARASUMA]
Sure.
I might have my share of doubts
about being a teacher.
But this place is really
starting to grow on me.
[KORO-SENSEI gurgling]
[OKANO]
Gross! Is that how he grovels?
[NAKAMURA] How badly
does he want this stuff?
--[OKANO, NAKAMURA scream]
--[KORO-SENSEI] Please, please!