Yuuki: HEY, GUYS!
THIS IS MISS ASUNA.
MISS ASUNA, THIS IS MY GUILD,
THE SLEEPING KNIGHTS!
Jun: MY NAME'S JUN.
WHAT'S UP? HOW'S IT GOING?
Talken: H‐HI, MISS ASUNA.
I‐I'M TALKEN.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU‐‐
AH!
Nori: YOU REALLY NEED
TO GET A GRIP
ON THOSE NERVES, TAL, SERIOUSLY.
EVERY TIME YOU MEET A GIRL,
YOU TURN INTO A BLUBBERING MESS.
ANYWAY, MY NAME'S NORI.
GLAD TO MEET YA.
Siune: MY NAME IS SIUNE.
IT'S WONDERFUL TO MEET YOU,
AND THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR COMING TODAY.
Tecchi: IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU.
MY NAME'S TECCHI.
Yuuki: AND...
I'M YUUKI, THE LEADER
OF THIS GUILD, KINDA, SORTA.
MISS ASUNA, DON'T LAUGH,
BUT SEE,
WE WANNA BE THE ONLY GUILD
TO BEAT THE BOSS ON THIS FLOOR,
AND WE WANT YOU TO HELP US!
Asuna: HUH?
(GASPS)
HUH?!
Yuuki: (CHUCKLES)
Asuna: THAT'S VERY AMBITIOUS,
BUT A BOSS RAID USUALLY TAKES
AT LEAST FORTY‐NINE PLAYERS.
THAT'S SEVEN PARTIES
WITH SEVEN PLAYERS APIECE,
SO NO MATTER
HOW SKILLED YOU ARE,
WITH JUST SEVEN PLAYERS,
THAT'S KIND OF‐‐
WELL, TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST,
IT'S UNREALISTIC.
Yuuki: YEAH,
IT SORTA IS, ISN'T IT?
WE TRIED TAKING ON THE BOSSES
ON FLOOR TWENTY‐FIVE
AND ‐SIX THE SAME WAY.
Asuna: HUH?! J‐JUST YOU SIX?
Yuuki: YUP.
AND IF YOU ASK ME, WE PUT UP
A PRETTY GOOD FIGHT, TOO,
BUT BOTH TIMES,
THIS HUGE GUILD SWOOPED IN
AND BEAT 'EM BEFORE WE
COULD FIGURE OUT OUR NEXT MOVE.
Asuna: WHY WOULD YOU
EVEN RISK IT?
Siune: THAT'S A STORY.
IT GOES BACK TO WHEN WE MET
IN ANOTHER GAME'S NET COMMUNITY.
WE HIT IT OFF RIGHT AWAY, AND
WE'VE BEEN FRIENDS EVER SINCE.
BUT WE ONLY HAVE
UNTIL NEXT SPRING
TO GO ON QUESTS TOGETHER.
SINCE OUR TIME'S LIMITED,
WE WANTED
TO MAKE THE MOST OF IT.
YOU SEE, COME SPRING,
WE'LL ALL
BE BUSY WITH OTHER THINGS,
SO WE DECIDED THAT BEFORE
WE DISBANDED THE GUILD,
WE HAD TO DO
SOMETHING SO AMAZING,
SO UNBELIEVABLE
WE'D REMEMBER IT FOREVER.
Nori: MM‐HMM.
Asuna: SO THAT'S WHY YOU
WANT TO DO THIS BOSS RAID.
Siune: EXACTLY!
IF WE DEFEAT A BOSS TOGETHER,
OUR NAMES WILL BE INSCRIBED
ON THE MONUMENT OF SWORDSMEN,
YOU KNOW, THE ONE
IN THE TOWN OF BEGINNINGS,
IN THE BLACK IRON PALACE.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS SILLY
AND MAYBE EVEN A LITTLE VAIN,
BUT WE REALLY WANT
TO GET OUR NAMES
UP ON THAT WALL, NO MATTER WHAT.
BUT GETTING THEM ON THERE'S
THE HARD PART.
Asuna: HMM?
Siune: IF A BOSS
IS DEFEATED BY A PARTY,
THEN ALL OF ITS MEMBERS
WILL GET THEIR NAMES
INSCRIBED ON THE MONUMENT,
BUT IF IT'S BEATEN BY MULTIPLE
PARTIES WORKING IN TANDEM,
ONLY THE NAMES OF
THE PARTY LEADERS GET INSCRIBED.
Asuna: OH.
Siune: THAT'S THE CATCH.
IF WE WANT
THE NAMES OF EVERYONE
IN THE SLEEPING KNIGHTS
UP ON THAT WALL,
WE HAVE TO BEAT THE BOSS
TOGETHER, JUST US, NO ONE ELSE,
SO WE TALKED IT OVER
AND CAME UP WITH A PLAN.
A PARTY CAN HAVE
UP TO SEVEN PLAYERS MAX,
THEREFORE WE DECIDED
TO FIND SOMEONE AS STRONG
OR EVEN STRONGER THAN
OUR MOST POWERFUL PLAYER, YUUKI,
AND HOPE WHOEVER WE FOUND
ACCEPTED OUR INVITATION.
Asuna: I GET IT.
THAT'S WHY YOU WERE DUELING.
Siune: WELL? WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT JOINING UP WITH US?
WE CAN'T PAY YOU VERY MUCH,
BUT YOU'RE WELCOME
TO WHAT WE HAVE.
Asuna: UH, OH, NO, THAT'S OKAY!
BOSS RAIDS
COST A FORTUNE AS IT IS,
SO YOU SHOULD USE
YOUR MONEY FOR THAT.
I'D FEEL HORRIBLE
TAKING YOUR MONEY, REALLY.
IF YOU WANT, YOU COULD GIVE ME
WHATEVER THE BOSS DROPS,
AND I'LL BE FINE.
Siune: REALLY?!
THEN YOU'LL JOIN OUR PARTY?
Sleeping Knights: (LAUGHING)
Asuna: HUH.
(THINKING) THIS IS NOTHING
LIKE HOW THE OLD AINCRAD WAS,
AND YET HERE I AM
THINKING ABOUT SAFETY MARGINS
AND THE ODDS OF WINNING,
HAVING SAFE FIGHTS
AND CERTAIN VICTORIES.
THERE'S MORE FUN
TO GAMES THAN THAT.
I BET YUUKI AND HER FRIENDS
ALREADY KNOW THIS
BETTER THAN I DO.
OKAY, LET'S SEE
HOW FAR WE CAN GO.
‐ Jun: YES!
‐ Tecchi: AWESOME.
Asuna: IN THE END, IT'S NOT
ABOUT WINNING OR LOSING.
IT'S HAVING FU‐‐
Yuuki: THANKS A BUNCH,
MISS ASUNA!
Asuna: (CHUCKLES) PLEASE,
I‐I'D PREFER IT IF YOU
JUST CALLED ME ASUNA.
Yuuki: (GIGGLES)
THEN YOU CAN CALL ME YUUKI.
Nori: SO, WHAT DO YA THINK?
SHE'S CUTE, HUH?
Asuna: THAT REMINDS ME,
MS. YUUKI‐‐SORRY, YUUKI...
THE DUEL WAS ALL ABOUT
TESTING PLAYERS, RIGHT?
Yuuki: YUP. PRETTY MUCH.
THEN YOU MUST'VE GONE UP AGAINST
A TON OF STRONG PLAYERS
BEFORE I SHOWED UP.
DO YOU REMEMBER EVER FIGHTING
A SPRIGGAN, DRESSED IN BLACK?
HE WOULD'VE BEEN USING
A ONE‐HANDED SWORD.
Yuuki: HUH.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I DO.
MAN, HE WAS PRETTY TOUGH.
Asuna: THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU
ASK HIM TO HELP YOU OUT?
Yuuki: MM, I DON'T KNOW.
HE JUST WASN'T RIGHT.
Asuna: WELL, WHY NOT?
Yuuki: HE FOUND OUT MY SECRET.
I CAN'T HAVE THAT.
Asuna: OKAY, SO FOR TOMORROW,
HOW 'BOUT WE MEET
BACK HERE AT 1:00?
‐ Jun: YOU GOT IT!
‐ Yuuki: YOU GOT IT!
‐ Tecchi: ROGER THAT.
‐ Siune: WHAT THEY SAID.
Asuna: AND LET'S HAVE FUN.
Sleeping Dragons: RIGHT!
Asuna: (CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
(THRUMMING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHING)
WH‐‐
MOM? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
Kyoko: LAST MONTH,
WHEN YOU WERE LATE FOR DINNER,
I TOLD YOU
IT BETTER NOT HAPPEN AGAIN.
AND HERE WE ARE.
YOU'RE LATE
BECAUSE OF THAT GAME,
SO NOW YOU LOSE YOUR PRIVILEGES.
Asuna: I JUST
LOST TRACK OF TIME.
THAT'S MY FAULT, AND I'M SORRY.
BUT YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO GO AND
PULL THE PLUG ON ME LIKE THAT.
YOU COULD'VE SHAKEN ME
OR EVEN YELLED IN MY EAR.
I WOULD'VE GOTTEN
AN ALERT IN‐GAME,
AND THEN
I COULD'VE LOGGED OUT‐‐
Kyoko: I TRIED
THAT APPROACH BEFORE.
IT TOOK YOU FIVE MINUTES
TO SNAP OUT OF IT, REMEMBER?
Asuna: WELL, YEAH.
I HAD TO SAY GOOD‐BYE
TO EVERYONE BEFORE I LOG‐‐
Kyoko: OH, DON'T GIVE ME THAT.
WHAT YOU DO
IN SOME STUPID VIRTUAL GAME
DOES NOT TAKE PRIORITY
OVER YOUR COMMITMENTS
IN THE REAL WORLD, EVER.
Asuna: I'M SORRY.
I'LL BE MORE CAREFUL NEXT TIME.
Kyoko: THIS WILL BE
YOUR LAST WARNING.
IF YOU BREAK YOUR WORD TO ME
BECAUSE OF THAT THING AGAIN,
I'M CONFISCATING IT.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S GOING ON
IN THAT HEAD OF YOURS.
YOU LOST TWO YEARS OF YOUR LIFE
BECAUSE OF THAT‐‐
THAT INFERNAL MACHINE.
YOU COULD'VE DIED.
HOW CAN YOU EVEN STAND
TO LOOK AT IT?
Asuna: (SIGHS)
THIS ISN'T THE NERVEGEAR,
MOTHER.
Kyoko: IT'S DINNERTIME.
GET CHANGED,
AND COME DOWNSTAIRS.
Asuna: I'M NOT HUNGRY.
Kyoko: AS YOU WISH.
(DOOR BEEPS)
(SHUDDERS)
HMM.
Yuuki: SOUNDS LIKE
A GOOD LINEUP, RIGHT?
HUH? ASUNA.
Asuna: (GASPS)
UH, S‐SO YUUKI, JUN,
AND TECCHI ARE UP FRONT.
THEN TALKEN AND NORI
ARE MIDRANGE,
AND SIUNE,
YOU'RE THE BACKUP? RIGHT.
THEN I GUESS, IF YOU'RE COVERED,
MAYBE I SHOULD HANG BACK
AS THE REARGUARD.
Yuuki: YEAH, SORRY.
I FEEL BAD YOU'RE NOT UP FRONT
WHEN YOU'RE SO GOOD
WITH A SWORD.
Asuna: OH, I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
I'M AFRAID
I'M NOT MUCH GOOD AS A TANK.
AND ANYWAY, I'M CURIOUS
TO SEE WHETHER JUN AND TECCHI
CAN SURVIVE A PROPER BEATDOWN.
Both: (STAMMER)
Jun: DON'T WORRY ABOUT US!
WE CAN HANDLE IT.
Asuna: I GUESS WE'LL SEE.
Jun: I HOPE.
Sleeping Dragons: (LAUGH)
Asuna: ALL RIGHT, READY TO GO
TAKE A PEEK AT THAT BOSS ROOM?
Sleeping Dragons: YEAH!
(WEAPONS CLASHING)
Yuuki: (YELLS)
‐ Jun: YEAH!
‐ Yuuki: YEAH!
(LAUGHTER)
Asuna: WHAT A TEAM.
I WONDER IF THEY
REALLY NEED ME AFTER ALL.
(SIGHS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW QUICKLY
YOU GUYS
ARE CLEARING THE LABYRINTH.
YOU'RE AN AMAZING GROUP
OF PLAYERS.
Yuuki: (LAUGHS)
(GASPS)
IT'S THE BOSS ROOM! COME ON!
Asuna: YUUKI, HOLD IT!
Yuuki: (GASPS)
Asuna: ECK, KAA‐RAH,
PHIM, FISCKLE,
BRYOTAH, RYU‐GAH, GARDOL.
Sleeping Knights: (GASPING)
Nori: (GASPS)
LOOK!
Players: (GASPING)
Player: W‐W‐WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA. HANG ON!
HANG ON!
WE'RE NOT HERE TO FIGHT YOU!
Asuna: THEN LOWER
YOUR WEAPONS NOW!
Player: GET RID OF IT.
Asuna: KEEP YOUR EYE ON THEM,
AND IF THEY MAKE A MOVE
FOR THEIR WEAPONS,
HIT 'EM
WITH AN AQUA BIND SPELL.
Siune: YOU GOT IT. (LAUGHS)
THIS IS OUR
FIRST‐EVER P. V. P. IN "A. L. O."
IT'S KIND OF THRILLING.
Asuna: IF YOU'RE NOT PK‐ers,
THEN WHY WERE
YOU HIDING FROM US?
Player: WE WERE
WAITING FOR SOMEONE.
WE WERE HIDING, 'CAUSE WE
DIDN'T WANNA GET HIT BY A MOB
BEFORE OUR FRIENDS GOT HERE.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
‐ Asuna: ALL RIGHT, THEN.
‐ Player 2: (SIGHS)
Asuna: WE'RE HERE
TO TAKE ON THE BOSS,
SO IF YOU'RE NOT READY
TO ENTER YET,
WE'D LIKE
TO TAKE A CRACK AT IT FIRST.
Player 1: N‐NO, THAT'S COOL.
WE'LL JUST HANG HERE,
YOU KNOW,
TILL OUR BUDDIES SHOW UP.
OH, AND, UH,
WATCH YOUR BACKS IN THERE.
GOOD LUCK.
Player 2: OATH, SHAAL,
OH‐BIS, GLONE, LOPT!
Jun: DON'T GIVE THOSE DUDES
A SECOND THOUGHT.
COME ON. LET'S DO THIS.
‐ Yuuki: HMM.
‐ Asuna: DON'T WORRY.
LET'S JUST STICK TO THE PLAN
AND HAVE A LOOK INSIDE, OKAY?
Yuuki: OKAY.
Jun: INSTEAD OF
JUST SCOPING IT OUT,
LET'S BUST IN THERE
AND TRASH THE BOSS.
Asuna: IF YOU WANT TO TRY,
GO FOR IT.
JUST MAKE SURE NOT TO USE
ANY OF YOUR EXPENSIVE POTIONS
AND STUFF TO RECOVER.
SIUNE AND I WILL SUPPORT YOU
WITH HEALING SPELLS,
SO FIGHT HARD, BUT TRY
NOT TO GET TOO FAR IN THE RED.
Jun: HA! RIGHT ON, COACH! UHH!
(LAUGHTER)
Asuna: LISTEN UP.
IF YOU DIE,
DON'T RESPAWN RIGHT AWAY.
JUST HANG OUT, AND STUDY
THE BOSS' ATTACK PATTERNS.
THEN LET'S MEET BACK
AT THE LOMBARD SAVE POINT
AND TALK ABOUT
WHAT WE LEARNED, OKAY?
Sleeping Knights: ROGER THAT!
(DOORS CREAKING)
Boss: (ROARING)
Asuna: LET'S GET HIM!
Sleeping Knights: RIGHT!
Nori: JEEZ!
WE GOT OUR BUTTS KICKED!
WHAT KINDA ATTACK WAS THAT?
THAT'S GOTTA BE
AGAINST THE RULES!
Tecchi: THAT BOSS SURE KNOWS
HOW TO DEFEND ITSELF.
YOU THINK THAT'S A RANDOM MOVE,
USING HIS ARMS TO BLOCK?
Yuuki: (GROANS)
AND WE FOUGHT SO HARD, TOO.
HEY! WHAT'S WRONG?!
‐ Tecchi: HMM?
‐ Jun: HMM?
Asuna: COME HERE, YOU GUYS.
GATHER ROUND.
‐ Nori: EH?
‐ Siune: EH?
Asuna: I KNOW YOU'RE TIRED,
BUT WE NEED TO TALK.
REMEMBER THOSE THREE GUYS
STANDING BY THE BOSS ROOM?
Siune: SURE. WHY?
Asuna: THEY WERE SCOUTS
FROM A GUILD
THAT SPECIALIZES IN BOSS RAIDS.
Sleeping Knights: (GASP)
Asuna: IF ANOTHER GUILD
TRIES TO HIT THAT BOSS ROOM,
THEIR JOB
IS TO SIT BACK AND WATCH.
THE BOSSES YOU TRIED TO RAID
ON THE PREVIOUS FLOOR
AND THE ONE BEFORE THAT,
I HAVE A FEELING
THEY WERE THERE, TOO.
Siune: I HAD NO IDEA
THEY WERE EVEN THERE.
Asuna: THEY DIDN'T GET
IN OUR WAY OR TRY TO STOP US,
SO THEY'RE DEFINITELY SPIES.
ALL THEY WANT IS INTEL.
AND WHEN A SMALL GUILD
LIKE THE SLEEPING KNIGHTS
COMES ALONG TO TAKE ON A BOSS,
WE'RE HELPING THEM FIGURE OUT
ALL ITS ATTACK PATTERNS
AND WEAKNESSES.
Talken: WAIT A SEC.
THE DOOR SHUT BEHIND US
WHEN WE WERE INSIDE,
AND THEY DEFINITELY
DIDN'T FOLLOW US,
SO IF THEY CAN'T SEE US
FIGHTING THE BOSS,
HOW ARE THEY GONNA GATHER
ANY INTEL ON IT?
Asuna: ACTUALLY,
THEY COULD SEE US FIGHT.
TOWARDS THE END THERE,
I LOOKED OVER,
AND I SAW A TINY GRAY LIZARD
NEAR JUN'S FEET.
THAT'S WHEN I REALIZED
I LET MY GUARD DOWN TOO SOON.
IT'S A DARK SPELL
CALLED PEEPING.
IT BINDS A FAMILIAR TO A PLAYER,
AND THE CASTER SEES
WHAT IT SEES.
Yuuki: SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS AFTER WE GOT HAMMERED
BY THE BOSSES
ON FLOORS TWENTY‐FIVE AND ‐SIX,
THAT OTHER GUILD
SWOOPING IN AND BEATING 'EM,
THAT WASN'T A COINCIDENCE?
Asuna: NO, I'M AFRAID IT WASN'T.
YOU PROBABLY FOUGHT SO HARD,
THE BOSS USED
EVERY MOVE IT HAD AGAINST YOU,
AND THEY SAW IT ALL.
THAT'S HOW THEY BEAT
THE BOSSES SO QUICKLY.
Siune: THEY USED US AGAIN.
NOW THEY KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT THIS BOSS, TOO.
THEY'RE PROBABLY IN THERE
TAKING IT DOWN.
Nori: THOSE DICKS.
Jun: DAMN IT.
Asuna: EASY, GUYS.
DON'T COUNT US OUT JUST YET.
Yuuki: BUT WHAT CAN WE DO
ABOUT IT NOW?
Asuna: SIMPLE. IT'S 2:30 P.M.
IN THE REAL WORLD.
AT THIS TIME OF DAY
AND ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE,
IT'LL BE HARD TO FIND
ENOUGH PEOPLE FOR A RAID PARTY.
BY MY ESTIMATE, IT SHOULD
TAKE THEM AT LEAST AN HOUR.
THAT'S PLENTY OF TIME FOR US.
SO HERE'S THE DEAL.
AFTER THIS,
IF WE CAN GET BACK TO THAT ROOM
IN THIRTY MINUTES,
WE CAN TAKE IT.
OKAY?
Sleeping Knights: (LAUGHING)
Yuuki: YEAH!
Jun: LAST ONE THERE'S
A ROTTEN EGG! (LAUGHS)
Yuuki: HEY! WAIT FOR US!
Jun: SLOWPOKE!
‐ Asuna: (laughs)
‐ Siune: (laughs)
Players: (MURMURING)
Yuuki: CRAP! WE'RE TOO LATE.
(SIGHS)
Asuna: DON'T WORRY.
THEY WON'T ADVANCE
WITH ONLY TWENTY PLAYERS.
WE SHOULD HAVE ENOUGH TIME
TO GIVE IT ONE MORE TRY
BEFORE THE REST SHOW UP.
Yuuki: YOU THINK?
‐ Asuna: EXCUSE ME!
‐ Player 3: HM?
Asuna: WE'D LIKE TO TRY
THE BOSS BEFORE YOU DO.
COULD YOU GUYS LET US BY?
Player 3: SORRY, DOLL‐FACE.
THE BOSS ROOM'S
OFF‐LIMITS FOR NOW.
Asuna: WAIT. OFF‐LIMITS?
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
Player 3: IT MEANS,
IN A COUPLE MINUTES,
THE REST OF THE GUILD'S
GONNA ROLL UP HERE.
WE'RE JUST HOLDING THE ROOM
TILL THEY DO.
IF YOU WANT,
YOU CAN WAIT OVER THERE.
Asuna: AND HOW LONG
DO YOU EXPECT US TO WAIT?
Player 3: UM...
ANOTHER HOUR OR SO.
Asuna: BUT WE DON'T HAVE
THAT KIND OF TIME!
IF YOU WERE GOING IN RIGHT NOW,
WELL, THAT'S A DIFFERENT STORY,
BUT YOU'RE NOT,
SO LET US GO IN FIRST.
Player 3: LOOK,
I DON'T MAKE THE RULES.
I'M JUST A GRUNT HERE,
FOLLOWING ORDERS
LIKE EVERYONE ELSE, OKAY?
YOU GOT A COMPLAINT,
GO TO THE GUILD HEADQUARTERS,
AND TALK TO THEM.
IT'S OVER IN YGG CITY, SO GET‐‐
Asuna: ARE YOU KIDDING?
THAT'S FAR AWAY!
IT'D TAKE US AT LEAST
AN HOUR TO GET THERE!
Yuuki: HEY, BIG GUY.
Player 3: HMM?
Yuuki: JUST TRYING
TO FIGURE THINGS OUT HERE.
SO NO MATTER HOW NICE WE ASK,
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
LET US GET BY YOU.
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
Player 3: YEAH, THAT'S IT.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH
WHAT I'M SAYING.
Yuuki: OKAY. IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING...
YOU WANNA FIGHT?
‐ Player 3: HUH?
‐ Asuna: HUH?
Players: (GASPING)
Asuna: BUT, YUUKI, ARE YOU SURE?
Yuuki: ASUNA,
SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA FIGHT
TO GET YOUR POINT ACROSS,
YOU KNOW, LIKE HOW DEAD SERIOUS
YOU ARE ABOUT SOMETHING.
JUST SAYING.
Jun: YUP,
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH HOW IT IS!
Asuna: YOU GUYS.
Player 3: (GASPS)
Yuuki: THESE FOLKS KNOW
EXACTLY WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THEY LOOK LIKE
THE SERIOUS TYPES.
WE COULD CHOP AWAY ALL DAY,
AND THEY'D DEFEND THIS ROOM
TO THE LAST PLAYER.
RIGHT, BIG GUY?
Player 3: UH...
W‐WE GOT ORDERS TO...
Yuuki: COME ON, DRAW YOUR SWORD.
Player 3: (GROWLS)
Y‐YOU LITTLE PUNK.
I'M GONNA MAKE YOU PAY FOR THAT.
Players: (MURMURING)
Asuna: (GASPS)
Yuuki: SOMETIMES YOU GOTTA FIGHT
TO GET YOUR POINT ACROSS.
Asuna: YEAH...
SHE'S RIGHT.
Yuuki: (CHUCKLES)
‐ Player 3: (CHUCKLES)
‐ Player 4: (CHUCKLES)
Nori: HEY, GUYS!
Asuna: I SHOULD'VE DEALT
WITH THIS WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
Yuuki: SORRY, ASUNA.
MY BIG MOUTH
GOT YOU INTO THIS MESS.
BUT IT WAS TOTALLY WORTH IT.
KNOW WHY? 'CAUSE JUST NOW,
I SAW THE BEST SMILE
I'VE EVER SEEN ON YOU!
Asuna: IN THAT CASE,
I'LL START PULLING MY WEIGHT.
WE MIGHT NOT
TAKE DOWN THIS BOSS,
BUT THE NEXT ONE,
I PROMISE THAT ONE'S OURS!
Player 5: EH?
HEH. SOME FOLKS
JUST DON'T KNOW WHEN TO QUIT.
Players: (GASP)
Kirito: SORRY, GUYS.
Asuna: (GASPING)
Kirito: STAND DOWN.
YOU'RE NOT GETTING PAST ME.