(SCHOOL BELL CHIMING)
Girl: ASADA!
SHINO ASADA!
Shopgirl: ALL YOUR FAVORITES
ARE IN STOCK RIGHT NOW.
Girl 2: MOVE.
GO ON.
QUIT DRAGGIN' YOUR FEET!
Endo: I NEED A FAVOR.
WE SORTA WENT
OVER‐TIME AT KARAOKE,
AND NOW WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH CASH FOR THE TRAIN HOME.
WE'RE GONNA NEED ABOUT TEN.
WE'LL PAY YOU BACK, THOUGH.
Sinon: TEN THOUSAND?
I DON'T HAVE
THAT MUCH MONEY ON ME.
Endo: WELL,
GO WITHDRAW IT THEN.
Sinon: NO.
Endo: HUH?
Sinon: YOU HEARD. I SAID NO.
I'M NOT GIVING YOU GUYS
ANY MONEY.
Endo: YOU BITCH.
WE'LL DO THIS THE HARD WAY.
Sinon: GET OUT OF THE WAY.
I WANNA GO.
Endo: (LAUGHS)
Sinon: (GASPS)
(WHIMPERING)
Endo: BANG.
(CHUCKLES) POOR ASADA.
Y'KNOW MY BIG BROTHER?
WELL, HE'S GOT A BUTT‐LOAD
OF THESE MODEL GUNS.
WOULDN'T IT BE COOL
IF I BROUGHT SOME TO CLASS?
I KNOW YOU LIKE GUNS,
ESPECIALLY PISTOLS.
Girl 2: UH‐OH.
SOMEONE'S GONNA HURL.
Girl 1: REMEMBER WHEN YOU BLEW
CHUNKS IN CLASS AND FAINTED?
OH, GOD, THAT STANK
LIKE ASS FOR DAYS.
Endo: ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS GIVE US YOUR MONEY,
AND WE'LL LET YOU GO HOME.
DON'T YA WANNA?
I MEAN, YOU LOOK LIKE HELL.
Kyoji: OFFICER!
A GIRL'S GETTING MUGGED
IN THE ALLEY! HURRY!
Endo: BITCH!
Sinon: (PANTING)
Kyoji: ASADA.
ARE YOU OKAY?
Sinon: YEAH,
I'M FINE, SHINKAWA.
THANKS FOR THAT.
Kyoji: SO I HEARD
WHAT HAPPENED THE OTHER DAY.
YOU WENT ON QUITE THE RAMPAGE.
Sinon: YEAH, BUT FOR
A STRATEGY, IT WAS A FAIL.
I MEAN,
WE STARTED THE OP WITH SIX
AND LOST FOUR
BY THE END OF IT.
IF THAT'S THE OUTCOME
OF AN AMBUSH WE SET UP,
IT'S NOT MUCH
OF A WIN, Y'KNOW?
Kyoji: YOU WERE PRETTY RAD,
THOUGH.
Y'KNOW THAT BEHEMOTH GUY
WITH THE MINIGUN?
HE WAS KIND OF A LEGEND
IN THE GAME,
'CAUSE HE NEVER BOUGHT IT
IN A SQUAD FIGHT BEFORE.
Sinon: YEAH?
I HAD NO IDEA
HE WAS THAT GOOD.
I NEVER REALLY SAW
HIS RANKINGS IN B. O. B.
Kyoji: HIS DAYS WERE NUMBERED.
I MEAN, NO MATTER
HOW POWERFUL A MINIGUN IS,
CARRYING
FIVE HUNDRED ROUNDS OF AMMO
PUSHES YOU
OVER THE WEIGHT LIMIT,
SO YOU CAN'T RUN.
AND SINCE B. O. B.'s
A SOLO ENCOUNTER BATTLE,
HE WAS EASY PICKINGS
FOR A SNIPER LIKE YOU.
STILL, WITH THAT GUN,
HE'S PRETTY MUCH INVINCIBLE
AS LONG AS HE'S
WITH A GOOD SQUAD.
THE MINIGUN
SHOULD BE BANNED
Sinon: IF WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT BANNING WEAPONS,
DON'T FORGET SOME PEOPLE THINK
MY HECATE'S A CHEAT, TOO.
AS ITS OWNER, I HAVE TO ADMIT
USING IT DOES HAVE
ITS OWN SPECIAL PROBLEMS.
Kyoji: (SIGHS) WISH I HAD
PROBLEMS LIKE THAT.
SO WHAT'RE YOUR PLANS
FOR THE NEXT B. O. B.?
Sinon:
I'M DEFINITELY ENTERING.
I DID MY HOMEWORK
AND HAVE MOST OF THE INFO
OF THE TOP TWENTY PLAYERS
FROM THE LAST ONE,
AND I'VE GOT MY HECATE NOW.
WITH HER IN MY HANDS,
I'M SURE I CAN KI‐‐
I‐I MEAN
CRACK THE HIGHER RANKS.
(THINKING) IF I CAN
TAKE OUT ALL MY ENEMIES
AND PROVE I'M THE STRONGEST,
I'LL BE FREE.
Kyoji: MAN...
ASADA, YOU'RE AMAZING.
HAVING THAT AWESOME GUN
IS ONE THING,
BUT YOU WERE ALSO SMART ENOUGH
TO PUT YOUR POINTS
ON STRENGTH STATS
SO YOU COULD USE IT.
I'M THE ONE
WHO GOT YOU INTO G. G. O.,
BUT I'VE BEEN
TOTALLY LEFT BEHIND.
Sinon: THAT IS SO NOT TRUE.
IN THE LAST QUALIFIER,
YOU MADE IT ALL THE WAY
TO THE SEMIFINALS, REMEMBER?
Kyoji: EH. WHATEVER.
AN AGI BUILD ONLY GETS YOU
SO FAR IN G. G. O.
A GOOD GUN HELPS, TOO.
I SPENT POINTS
ON THE WRONG STAT.
Sinon: DON'T GET SO DOWN
ABOUT THAT STUFF.
SIGN UP FOR B. O. B.,
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
Kyoji: NAH. NO POINT.
I'D JUST DIE.
Sinon: OH. HMM.
HEY, HOW'RE YOUR STUDIES
COMING ALONG?
YOU STILL WANNA BE A DOCTOR?
Kyoji: YEAH. IT IS
THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
I PROMISED MY DAD
I'D GO TO MED SCHOOL,
SO IT'S A DONE DEAL.
STUCK WITH IT NOW.
Sinon: WELL, WHAT ABOUT
CRAM SCHOOL AND THE G. E. D.?
ARE THOSE GOING OKAY?
Kyoji: OH, YEAH.
IT'S GOIN' GREAT.
I'M MAINTAINING THE SAME RANK
I HAD WHEN I WAS AT SCHOOL.
STAYIN' SHARP, MA'AM.
LOCKED AND LOADED.
Sinon: ROGER THAT.
(LAUGHING)
Kyoji: (LAUGHING)
Sinon: THE REASON I ASKED,
IS 'CAUSE YOU'RE ALWAYS
ONLINE WHEN I LOG ON.
THAT'S WHY I WAS
A LITTLE WORRIED.
IF YOU'RE ONLINE THAT MUCH,
WHEN DO YOU STUDY?
Kyoji: I DO MOST OF MY STUDYING
DURING THE DAY,
AND I TAKE LOTS OF BREAKS, TOO.
Sinon: YOU MUST BE
MAKING TONS OF CASH
IF YOU'RE DIVING
ALL THE TIME LIKE THAT.
Kyoji: I'M NOT MAKING THAT MUCH.
SOLO HUNTING'S IMPOSSIBLE
FOR AGI BUILDS THESE DAYS.
Sinon: OH. WELL,
YOU'RE DOING GREAT
IF YOU'RE EARNING ENOUGH
FOR THE CONNECTION FEE.
UH‐OH, IT'S LATE.
SORRY. I HAVE TO GET GOING NOW.
Kyoji: OH. OKAY. HEY, UH...
ARE YOU STILL MAKIN' DINNER
FOR YOURSELF?
I'D LOVE TO TRY MORE
OF YOUR COOKING SOMEDAY.
Sinon: HUH? OH, SURE.
OKAY.
IT'S JUST I THINK I NEED
TO GET BETTER AT IT FIRST.
THANKS FOR THE TEA.
AND THANKS‐‐I MEAN,
THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME.
YOU WERE PRETTY COOL.
Kyoji: I WISH I COULD ALWAYS
BE THERE TO PROTECT YOU.
HEY, UH, IF YOU WANT,
I CAN WALK YOU HOME
EVERY DAY.
I MEAN, IF YOU WANT.
Sinon: OH, NO, NO.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'LL BE FINE.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I'LL GET STRONGER.
WHAT A DAY.
I CAN DO THIS.
(NERVOUS BREATHING)
(HEART BEATING)
(SCREAMS)
I DON'T REMEMBER
WHAT DAD LOOKED LIKE.
I REMEMBER HEARING HE DIED
IN A CAR ACCIDENT, THOUGH,
SOMETIME BEFORE I TURNED TWO.
AFTER THE ACCIDENT,
MY MOM AND I LEFT TOKYO.
WE WENT TO GO LIVE
WITH HER PARENTS.
IT WAS PEACEFUL THERE
FOR BOTH OF US.
Ms. Asada: (CHUCKLES)
Young Sinon: HUH?
Sinon: AND THEN ONE DAY,
THAT PEACE WAS SHATTERED.
Robber: (GRUNTS)
PUT THE MONEY IN THE BAG,
GOD DAMN IT!
AND DON'T HIT THE ALARM,
OR ELSE!
Young Sinon: MOMMY!
Robber: C'MON!
DON'T JUST STAND THERE!
START FILLIN' IT UP!
LET'S GO! MOVE IT!
Clerk: OKAY, SURE.
(GUNSHOT)
Robber: I TOLD HIM NOT TO!
YOU HEARD ME!
LET'S GO, BITCH!
FILL IT UP,
OR YOU GET IT, TOO!
GIMME THE MONEY NOW,
OR I'M GONNA KILL HER NEXT!
I SWEAR I'LL DO IT!
(SCREAMS)
YOU LITTLE...
GIVE IT BACK, YOU BRAT! LET GO!
LET GO OF MY GUN!
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMS)
Sinon: (SCREAMING)
Robber: (LAUGHS)
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
Sinon: (VOMITS)
(COUGHING)
(VOMITS)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
I LOOK AWFUL
SOMEBODY...
ANYBODY SAVE ME.
Asuna: WAIT! WHAT?!
Y‐YOU'RE KIDDING!
YOU'RE QUITTING A. L. O.?!
Kirito: N‐NO!
I'LL JUST BE GONE
FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
I'LL CONVERT BACK AFTER THAT.
Asuna: BUT WHY?
Kirito: WELL, ACTUALLY...
IT'S COMPLICATED.
THERE'S THIS OTHER VIRTUAL MMO
THAT I NEED TO CHECK OUT.
Asuna: "NEED TO," HUH?
YOU'VE DONE THIS BEFORE
AND JUST USED NEW ACCOUNTS.
WHY NOT FOR THIS ONE, TOO?
I MEAN, IF YOU CONVERT,
YOUR ITEMS WILL BE RESET.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
Kirito:
WELL, IT'S LIKE A FAVOR
FOR THAT GUY
FROM THE GOVERNMENT.
Asuna: I GUESS IF MR. KIKUOKA'S
ASKING YOU TO,
YOU CAN'T SAY NO.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT IS ABOUT THAT MAN,
BUT THERE'S A PART OF ME
THAT STILL HAS
A HARD TIME TRUSTING HIM.
Kirito: YEAH. I'M NOT TOO SURE
I CAN TRUST HIM, EITHER.
Asuna: JUST GET BACK
AS SOON AS YOU CAN.
THIS IS OUR HOME,
AND IT'S NOT THE SAME
WITHOUT YOU.
(GEAR CLANKING)
Kirito: DON'T WORRY.
I'LL BE BACK IN A.L.O.
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
I'LL JUST DIVE
INTO GUN GALE ONLINE
FOR A COUPLE DAYS,
SEE WHAT'S GOIN' ON,
AND THAT'S THAT.
I'M NINETY‐NINE PERCENT SURE
THE DEATH GUN STORY'S A HOAX,
PROBABLY SOMEONE TROLLING.
YOU CAN'T KILL SOMEONE
IN THE REAL WORLD
FROM THE VIRTUAL ANYMORE.
I KNOW THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
Death Gun:
THIS IS REAL POWER,
REAL STRENGTH!
LET YOUR FEAR CARVE ONE NAME
INTO YOUR BRAINS,
THE NAME I SHARE
WITH THIS WEAPON,
DEATH GUN!
Kirito: BUT THERE'S STILL
THAT ONE PERCENT CHANCE
IT COULD BE TRUE.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
HELLO. ANYONE HERE?
Aki: YEP!
WHAT'S GOIN' ON, KIRIGAYA?
Kirito: MS. AKI.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
(GASPS)
Aki: WHOA!
YOU FINALLY
GOT SOME MEAT ON YOU.
YOU COULD USE SOME FILLING OUT,
THOUGH.
YOU SURE YOU'RE EATING RIGHT?
Kirito: YEAH, I'M EATING.
I'M EATING.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
Aki: YOUR FRIEND
IN THE SUIT AND GLASSES
TOLD ME ABOUT YOUR MISSION.
HE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT
YOU GOING INTO A VIRTUAL NETWORK
AND DOING SOME RECONNAISSANCE
OR SOMETHING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'D ASK YOU.
I MEAN, YOU'VE ONLY BEEN
BACK FOR A YEAR.
ANYWAY, HE FOUND OUT
I WAS THE ONE
WHO WAS IN CHARGE OF YOUR REHAB,
SO HE ASKED ME TO KEEP AN EYE
ON YOUR MONITORS WHILE YOU DIVE.
THEY TOOK ME OFF MY NORMAL SHIFT
AND EVERYTHING.
THE HEAD NURSE WASN'T HAPPY,
BUT WHAT CAN SHE DO ABOUT IT?
IF THE GOVERNMENT
WANTS SOMETHING,
THEY'RE GONNA GET IT.
WELL, I GUESS YOU AND ME
ARE BACK TOGETHER AGAIN, HUH?
Kirito: YEAH.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
UM, SO IT'S JUST US TODAY?
NO KIKUOKA?
Aki: MM‐HMM. HE ASKED ME
TO GIVE YOU A MESSAGE, THOUGH.
Kikuoka: EMAIL YOUR REPORTS
TO ME AT THE USUAL ADDRESS.
YOUR FEE AND EXPENSES
WILL BE PAID
WHEN YOU FINISH THE MISSION,
SO PLEASE DON'T FORGET
TO SEND ME AN INVOICE.
P.S. JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE ALONE
WITH A PRETTY NURSE,
YOU'RE STILL ON THE CLOCK.
TRY TO KEEP THOSE HORMONES
OF YOURS UNDER CONTROL.
Kirito: UH, IF IT'S OKAY,
I'D LIKE TO CONNECT
TO THE NETWORK NOW.
Aki: YEAH, SURE.
IT'S ALL SET UP.
OKAY, HOT STUFF, STRIP!
Kirito: WHY?!
Aki: FOR THE ELECTRODES.
OH, DON'T BE SHY.
I'VE SEEN
ALL YOUR GOODIES BEFORE.
Kirito: UH, ACTUALLY,
CAN I JUST TAKE OFF MY SHIRT?
Aki: MM‐HMM.
Kirito: (SIGHS)
Aki: THERE.
YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
Kirito: WELL, HERE I GO.
WISH ME LUCK.
I DON'T SEE THIS TAKIN' ME
MORE THAN FOUR OR FIVE HOURS.
Aki: YOU GOT IT.
AND DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT
YOUR BODY WHILE YOU'RE GONE.
I'LL KEEP
A CLOSE EYE ON IT.
Kirito: THANKS.
I FEEL BETTER ALREADY
LINK START!
Sinon: YEAH, I'M DOING GREAT.
I'M USED TO THE SCHOOL NOW,
AND I'VE MADE
SOME FRIENDS, TOO.
I'M FINE, REALLY.
I'VE ONLY HAD A COUPLE
PANIC ATTACKS. THAT'S ALL.
YEAH, GRANDPA, I WILL.
DON'T YOU CATCH
ANY COLDS, EITHER.
I'LL COME HOME
FOR WINTER BREAK.
ME, TOO. BYE.
EVER SINCE THAT DAY,
WHENEVER I SEE A GUN,
I FREAK OUT.
IF I SEE A PICTURE OF ONE
OR SEE ONE ON TV,
I'M GUARANTEED A PANIC ATTACK.
I CAME TO TOKYO
FOR HIGH SCHOOL,
THINKING IF I GOT FAR ENOUGH
AWAY FROM HOME, IT'D HELP,
BUT IT DIDN'T.
ONE DAY, SHINKAWA TOLD ME
ABOUT GUN GALE ONLINE,
AND I THOUGHT IT COULD WORK
AS A KIND OF THERAPY FOR ME.
AND IN A WAY, IT WORKED.
AS SINON,
WHEN I'M HOLDING A GUN
OR WHEN SOMEONE'S
DRAWING DOWN ON ME,
I CAN HANDLE IT.
I FIGURE
THE STRONGER SINON GETS,
THE STRONGER I'LL GET
IN THE REAL WORLD,
SO I KEEP FIGHTING
WITH MY HECATE TWO,
HOPING IT'LL HELP ME
KICK THIS PHOBIA.
WINNING THE NEXT
BULLET OF BULLETS WILL CURE ME.
I KNOW IT WILL.
IT HAS TO.
LINK START.
Player 1: ZXE‐D AND TARAKO
HAVEN'T LOGGED ON FOR A WHILE.
IT'S BEEN, LIKE, A MONTH.
IF ANYONE'S GOT THEIR
CONTACT INFO IN THE REAL WORLD,
HOOK US UP WITH IT.
Player 2: DUDE, IF NO ONE'S
HEARD FROM 'EM THIS LONG,
THEY'RE GONE FOR GOOD.
Player 3:
WE KNOW THE DATE AND TIME
THEY WERE SHOT
BY DEATH GUN, THOUGH,
SO ALL WE HAVE
TO DO IS CHECK
IF ANY VRMMO PLAYERS
DIED AROUND THAT TIME,
AND WE'LL KNOW
WHAT HAPPENED TO 'EM.
Player 1: YEAH,
BUT IF THEY LIVED ALONE,
MAYBE NO ONE'S FOUND
THEIR BODIES YET.
WE ALREADY ASKED THE COPS,
BUT THEY'RE NOT TALKING.
WE EVEN SENT EMAILS TO ZASKAR
ABOUT 'EM,
BUT ALL THEY SENT BACK
WAS THE OLD,
"SORRY, WE NEVER SHARE
OUR USERS' PERSONAL INFO" CRAP.
Player 3:
I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT THE ONLY WAY TO BE
SURE THEY WERE KILLED
IS FOR ONE OF US
TO SACRIFICE HIMSELF.
SO TOMORROW AT 11:30 P. M.,
I'M GONNA WAIT FOR DEATH GUN
AT THE GLOCKEN CENTRAL BANK,
AND JUST SO HE KNOWS IT'S ME,
I'LL HAVE A RED ROSE
ON MY CHEST.
SHOOT ME, DEATH GUN!
I DARE YOU.
Player 1: AH, DUDE,
YOU'LL BE A HERO.
BUT YOU BETTER POST
YOUR REAL NAME AND ADDRESS.
OTHERWISE, WHAT'S THE POINT?
Player 2: OH, DO A PUBLIC DIVE
AT AN INTERNET CAFE, MAN!
Player 1: (LAUGHING) DO IT!
DO IT!
Death Gun: WHATEVER.