(GUNFIRE)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Leafa: HMM, WHERE'S KAZUTO?
HE SHOULD HAVE SHOWN UP BY NOW.
Silica: MAYBE THEY DON'T HAVE
ALL THE BATTLES UP
ON THE FEED YET.
I MEAN, KNOWING KIRITO,
WE SHOULD HAVE SEEN HIM
RUNNING AROUND,
GUNS BLAZING FROM THE START.
Klein: I DON'T KNOW.
HE'S ONE OF THE CRAFTIEST
PLAYERS I'VE EVER MET.
HE'S PROBABLY
LAYING LOW SOMEWHERE,
WAITING FOR THE COMPETITION
TO KILL EACH OTHER OFF.
Asuna: OH, PLEASE.
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
HE DOESN'T PLAY LIKE THAT.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, YUI?
Yui: ABSOLUTELY.
BESIDES, DADDY'S SO FAST,
I DOUBT HE'LL EVEN
SHOW UP ON CAMERA.
HE'LL SNEAK UP AND STRIKE
BEFORE HIS ENEMY
KNOWS WHAT'S HAPPENING.
Lisbeth: (LAUGHS)
HE CAN'T DO IT ANY OTHER WAY.
I MEAN, IT'S A GAME WITH GUNS,
AND HE'S USING A SWORD.
WHAT A DOOFUS.
All: (LAUGH)
Klein: YEAH,
HE IS KIND OF A DORK.
‐ (GUNFIRE)
‐ Lisbeth: (WHISTLES)
THAT ONE GUY'S UNBELIEVABLE.
Asuna: HUH?
YOU MEAN THE ONE IN WHITE?
Dyne: (GROANS)
(GUNSHOT)
NO!
Girls: (GASP)
Silica: HE'S SUPER FAST.
Lisbeth: YEAH.
THAT GUY'S SICK.
I BET HE'S GONNA WIN THIS THING.
Girls: (GASP)
Klein: LOOKS LIKE YOUR BOY
IS FULL OF SUCK, LIZ.
Lisbeth: SHUT UP.
HE'S NOT OUT OF IT YET.
Silica: WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
Yui: IT'S SOME KIND
OF PARALYSIS ATTACK,
MOST LIKELY TEMPORARY.
Leafa: IT'S LIKE HE WAS HIT
WITH THAT WIND SPELL,
THUNDER WEB.
Girls: (GASP)
Kirito: (GASPS)
SINON, SHOOT.
Sinon: HUH? WHICH ONE?
Kirito: IT'S THE GUY
IN THE CLOAK.
THERE'S NO TIME! SHOOT HIM!
HURRY!
DON'T LET HIM FIRE THAT GUN!
Sinon: (GASPS)
OH, CRAP.
HE KNEW I WAS HERE.
Kirito: HOW COULD HE?
Sinon: MAYBE HE
SPOTTED ME EARLIER,
GOT MY POSITION
FROM THE LAST SCAN.
Both: (GASP)
(CRACKLING)
Sinon: JESUS. WHAT WAS THAT?
Girls: (GASP)
Death Gun:
DEATH GUN IS MY NAME
AND THE NAME OF MY GUN.
ONE DAY,
I'LL PAY YOU ALL A VISIT, TOO,
AND BRING REAL DEATH
WITH THIS GUN.
YOU'VE SEEN MY POWER.
IT IS REAL.
THIS ISN'T OVER, NOT YET.
I'M JUST GETTING STARTED.
IT'S SHOWTIME.
Asuna: I'VE MET
THAT PERSON BEFORE.
BUT WHERE?
THERE'S ONLY
ONE PLACE I COULD'VE,
AINCRAD.
Girls: (GASP)
Lisbeth: WAY TO SCARE
THE HELL OUTTA EVERYONE.
Klein: YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
NO WAY. CAN'T BE.
Asuna: YOU KNOW HIM, TOO?
DO YOU REMEMBER HIS NAME?
Klein: NO. I FORGET THE HANDLE
HE USED, BUT IT'S HIM.
THERE'S NO DOUBT.
HE WAS IN LAUGHING COFFIN.
Asuna: LAUGHING COFFIN.
WAS HE THEIR LEADER?
YOU KNOW, THE KNIFE WIELDER?
Klein: NO.
PRETTY SURE IT'S NOT POH.
SOMETHING ABOUT THE WAY THIS GUY
TALKS AND ACTS IS DIFFERENT.
EXCEPT FOR
THAT "SHOWTIME" LINE, THOUGH.
POH WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO SAID THAT.
BUT THIS GUY,
HE WAS CLOSE TO POH.
I'M TALKING
RIGHT‐HAND‐MAN CLOSE.
Asuna: KIRITO.
Kirito: IT'S HIM, ALL RIGHT.
OH, YEAH. THAT'S DEATH GUN.
Sinon: DEATH GUN?
YOU'RE JOKING.
YOU MEAN
THOSE RUMORS ABOUT PLAYERS
GETTING SHOT AND DISAPPEARING,
THOSE ARE ALL TRUE?
Kirito: YEAH, THEY ARE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW HE DOES IT YET,
BUT HE'S BEEN KILLING PLAYERS
IN THE REAL WORLD.
Sinon: THAT'S INSANE!
Kirito: IT'S NOT.
TWO PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN CONFIRMED DEAD.
WHERE'D HE GO?
(WATCH ALARM BEEPING)
Sinon: KIRITO,
WATCH THE BRIDGE FOR A SEC.
I'M GONNA CHECK THE SCAN AND
SEE WHAT NAME HE'S GOING BY.
Kirito: YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
Sinon: HUH?
WHERE IS HE?
COULD HE HAVE MOVED THAT FAST?
NO.
THIS IS OUR CHANCE.
Kirito: FOR WHAT?
Sinon: YOUR PAL IN THE CLOAK
ISN'T SHOWING UP
ON THE TERMINAL.
MY GUESS IS
HE JUMPED IN THE RIVER.
IF I'M RIGHT,
THEN HE HAD TO DISABLE
HIS GEAR LIKE YOU DID.
Kirito: WHAT ABOUT HIS HANDGUN?
HE CAN STILL MOVE UNDERWATER
WITH THAT EQUIPPED, RIGHT?
Sinon: EVEN IF HE COULD,
IT'S JUST ONE LITTLE HANDGUN.
I COULD TAKE HIM OUT EASY
WITH MY HECATE.
Kirito: YOU CAN'T!
YOU SAW WHAT HAPPENED.
HE USED THAT LITTLE GUN
TO KILL PALE RIDER.
ALL IT TAKES IS ONE SHOT.
GET IT? ONE SHOT,
AND YOU'RE DEAD FOR REAL!
Sinon: YEAH, WELL,
I'M NOT BUYING IT.
HOW'S IT EVEN POSSIBLE?
I MEAN, A PLAYER
KILLING PEOPLE I. R. L.?
Kirito: I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY,
BUT IT'S THE TRUTH.
THIS DEATH GUN GUY
KILLED A LOT OF PEOPLE
IN THAT V. R. M. M. O. I WAS IN.
WHEN HE USED HIS SWORD
ON SOMEONE,
HE KNEW HE WAS
REALLY KILLING 'EM.
AND SO DID I.
Sinon: THERE'S A KILLER,
A MURDERER, IN "GGO"?
Woman: (SCREAMS)
Robber: (LAUGHS)
Kirito: SINON.
SINON!
Sinon: (GASPS)
I'M ALL RIGHT,
JUST A LITTLE FREAKED OUT.
ANYWAY, I'M STILL NOT CONVINCED
WHAT YOU TOLD ME'S POSSIBLE,
BUT I DON'T THINK YOU'RE
LYING TO ME ABOUT IT, EITHER.
Kirito: THAT'S GOOD ENOUGH.
I CAN'T ASK FOR MORE.
Sinon: YEAH, WELL, WE BETTER
GET OUT OF THE AREA ASAP.
THE OTHERS KNOW
WE'RE HERE BY NOW.
THEY THINK WE'RE BUSY
FIGHTING EACH OTHER,
SO THEY'LL BE CLOSING IN SOON.
Kirito: YOU GOT A POINT.
WE'LL SPLIT UP HERE THEN.
Sinon: WAIT.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
Kirito: I'M GOING
AFTER DEATH GUN ALONE.
WHATEVER YOU DO,
STAY AWAY FROM HIM.
Sinon: BUT‐‐
Kirito: I'LL KEEP MY PROMISE.
NEXT TIME WE SEE EACH OTHER,
I'LL GIVE YOU
THE FIGHT I OWE YOU.
OH, AND ONE MORE THING,
THANKS FOR HEARING ME OUT
JUST NOW
INSTEAD OF SHOOTING ME
Sinon: HUH?
HEY!
(GROANS)
WAIT FOR ME!
I'M COMING WITH YOU.
Kirito: WHAT?
Sinon: THAT DEATH GUN GUY
SEEMS PRETTY TOUGH,
AND IF HE KILLS YOU,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO FIGHT ME.
Kirito: I DON'T THINK YOU GET‐‐
Sinon: LOOK, I'M NOT
A FAN OF TEAMING UP, EITHER,
BUT I THINK
WE STAND A BETTER CHANCE
OF KNOCKING THAT GUY
OUT OF THE GAME
IF WE WORK TOGETHER.
Kirito:
NO, I'M NOT DOWN WITH THAT.
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
Sinon: WE DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE HE'LL POP UP NEXT,
SO IT'LL BE DANGEROUS
WHETHER WE'RE TOGETHER OR NOT.
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
Kakouton: HUH?
Kirito: WE BETTER
TAKE CARE OF THIS JOKER.
I'LL BLOCK HIS BULLETS.
YOU WAIT FOR AN OPENING.
Sinon: ROGER THAT.
Kirito: HE'S ALL YOURS!
Kakouton: NO WAY.
Kirito: DEATH GUN'S PROBABLY
HEADING NORTH UP THE RIVER.
I WANNA BE THERE
WHEN HE SURFACES,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
WHERE HE'LL STOP.
GOT ANY IDEAS, SINON?
Sinon: UH...
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S GOT
ANY OTHER SPECIAL SKILLS,
BUT FROM WHAT I'VE SEEN,
HE'S A SNIPER.
HE'S GONNA AVOID OPEN SPACES
AND LOOK FOR A PLACE WITH COVER.
IF I WERE HIM, I'D SET MYSELF UP
IN THE RUINS OF THAT CITY.
Kirito: GOOD. THEN THAT'S
WHERE YOU AND ME ARE GONNA GO.
Sinon: ON YOUR SIX.
Klein: IN "S. A. O.,"
WE HAD A CODE.
NEVER LET ANOTHER PLAYER'S H. P.
HIT ZERO,
NO MATTER WHAT.
WE KNEW
IF IT DROPPED TO NOTHING,
THAT PLAYER WOULD DIE.
LAUGHING COFFIN DIDN'T CARE.
THEY KILLED DOZENS‐‐
NO, HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE.
THE ASSAULT TEAM
HAD TO STEP IN.
THEY PUT A PARTY TOGETHER
TO HUNT 'EM DOWN
AND CAPTURE THEM.
Leafa: AND KAZUTO
WAS THERE WITH YOU?
Kirito: YEAH. HE WAS UP FRONT,
GOING TOE TO TOE.
EVERYTHING WENT TO HELL
PRETTY FAST.
Leafa: OH, MAN.
THAT'S WHY KAZUTO'S
BEEN ACTING SO WEIRD LATELY.
NOW I'M WORRIED.
MAYBE HE'S TRYING TO SETTLE
SOME GRUDGE OR SOMETHING
Lisbeth: GRUDGE?
ISN'T THIS SUPPOSED
TO BE A PART‐TIME JOB?
Asuna: SORRY.
I'M LOGGING OUT FOR A BIT.
Silica: WHY?
Asuna: I HAVE TO GET IN TOUCH
WITH KIRITO'S CLIENT.
Silica: WAIT. HE'S GOT A CLIENT?
Asuna: MM‐HMM. HE'S THE ONE WHO
GOT KIRITO TO DIVE INTO "GGO."
I BET HE KNOWS WHAT'S GOING ON.
OH, AND, YUI, I'M GOING TO NEED
YOUR HELP WHILE I'M GONE.
FIND OUT
ANYTHING YOU CAN ABOUT "GGO."
Yui: YOU CAN COUNT ON ME, MOMMY!
Asuna: I'LL BE BACK
IN A LITTLE WHILE.
WISH ME LUCK.
Sinon: WHERE THE HECK DID HE GO?
YOU THINK WE MIGHT'VE PASSED HIM
ON THE WAY OVER HERE?
Kirito: NO, WE DIDN'T PASS HIM.
I WAS KEEPING AN EYE
ON THE RIVER
THE WHOLE TIME WE WERE RUNNING.
Sinon: OH.
WELL, THE RIVER DEAD‐ENDS HERE.
I GUESS
HE MUST BE LURKING AROUND
SOMEWHERE IN THE CITY NOW.
Kirito: OKAY.
LISTEN, WHEN HIS LOCATION
POPS UP IN THE NEXT SCAN,
WE'LL RUSH HIM
BEFORE HE CAN KILL ANYONE ELSE.
Sinon: I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
BUT THERE'S ONE PROBLEM.
HOW WILL WE KNOW
WHO DEATH GUN IS?
I MEAN, THAT'S NOT
HIS AVATAR'S HANDLE, REMEMBER?
Kirito: UH, OH, YEAH. RIGHT.
THEN LET'S START
WITH WHAT WE KNOW.
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T RECOGNIZE
THE NAMES OF THREE NEW PLAYERS.
IT'S NOT PALE RIDER,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
THAT LEAVES US WITH TWO NAMES
IN PLAY THAT COULD BE DEATH GUN,
JUSHI X AND STERBEN.
Sinon: IF THEY'RE
BOTH IN THE CITY,
WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO PICK THE WRONG ONE.
WAIT A SEC.
I JUST THOUGHT OF SOMETHING.
IN JAPANESE, THE "SHI"
IN "JUSHI" MEANS DEATH.
GET IT?
AND THE "X" COULD MEAN CROSS,
LIKE MAKING
THE SIGN OF THE CROSS!
YOU THINK?
OR MAYBE IT'S TOO OBVIOUS
Kirito: HMM. MAYBE NOT.
AREN'T AVATAR NAMES
USUALLY SIMPLE AND OBVIOUS?
MINE'S A VARIATION
ON MY REAL NAME.
AND YOURS?
Sinon: YEAH, SAME HERE.
Kirito:
WELL, IF THEY'RE BOTH HERE,
WE'LL GO AFTER JUSHI X FIRST.
OH, AND IF I GET PARALYZED
LIKE PALE RIDER, DON'T PANIC.
GET INTO POSITION, AND WAIT.
Sinon: HUH?
Kirito: DEATH GUN'S PROBABLY
HIDING SOMEWHERE CLOSE.
WHEN HE COMES OUT
TO FINISH ME OFF,
THAT'S WHEN YOU SHOOT HIM.
Sinon: AREN'T YOU WORRIED
I'LL SHOOT YOU, TOO?
Kirito: ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU'RE THE LAST PERSON
I'D EXPECT TO PLAY IT LIKE THAT.
LET'S GO, PARTNER.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU.
Sinon: OKAY, BUT ONCE
WE GET HIM, ALL BETS ARE OFF!
KIRITO, CHECK THE NORTH SIDE
OF THE MAP.
IT'S HIM.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE IN THE CITY.
I GUESS HE'S OUR MAN, HUH.
Kirito: YEAH.
I DON'T SEE STERBEN AROUND.
THAT SETTLES IT. JUSHI X AND
DEATH GUN ARE ONE AND THE SAME.
THAT MEANS HE'S GOING AFTER...
HIM.
Sinon: WE BETTER MOVE FAST.
RICOCO'S ALMOST IN RANGE.
Kirito: YEAH.
ARE YOU READY FOR THIS?
Sinon: YUP.
FOUND HIM. UP THERE.
Kirito: HE'S PROBABLY
WAITING FOR RICOCO
TO WALK RIGHT UP
INTO HIS SIGHTS.
I'LL ATTACK JUSHI X FROM BEHIND
WHILE I GOT THE CHANCE.
THAT BUILDING
IN FRONT OF THE STADIUM
MIGHT BE A GOOD PLACE
FOR YOU TO GET INTO POSITION.
Sinon: NO. I'M COMING WITH YOU.
Kirito: NOT THIS TIME.
I CAN FIGHT WAY BETTER
KNOWING YOU GOT MY BACK.
WE'RE A TEAM, REMEMBER?
Sinon: MM‐HMM.
Kirito: ALL I'M GONNA NEED
IS 30 SECONDS TO GET UP THERE,
AND I'LL BE READY
TO TAKE HIM OUT.
IS THAT ENOUGH TIME FOR YOU?
Sinon: MM‐HMM. PLENTY.
Kirito: COOL. SEE YOU IN A BIT.
Birds: (CAWING)
Sinon: SOON AS DEATH GUN'S GONE,
WE'LL BE ENEMIES AGAIN.
I'LL SHOOT HIM, BEAT HIM,
AND THEN FORGET HIM.
WHATEVER.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'LL EVER
SEE HIM AGAIN AFTER THIS.
WHAT?
BUT...
DEATH GUN'S SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THE STADIUM.
(GASPS)
Death Gun:
KIRITO, WHEREVER YOU ARE,
IT'S TIME I FOUND OUT IF YOU'RE
THE REAL DEAL OR A FAKE.
I REMEMBER
HOW YOU FOUGHT BACK THEN,
ALL FURY AND RAGE.
IF I KILL THIS FRIEND OF YOURS
AND YOU GO BERSERK
LIKE I REMEMBER,
I'LL KNOW IT'S REALLY YOU.
Sinon: HE'S GONNA KILL ME?
Death Gun: COME ON, KIRITO.
SHOW ME.
LET'S SEE YOUR FURY,
YOUR RAGE,
YOUR INSANE SWORD.
SHOW ME FOR OLD TIMES' SAKE.
Sinon: A TYPE 54 BLACK STAR.
IT'S THE GUN.
WHY?
WHY HERE?
WHY DOES HE HAVE THAT GUN?
Robber: (LAUGHS)
(HEART BEATING)
(GUNSHOT ECHOES)