(GUNSHOT)
(RIFLE CLICKS)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
Monster: (SHRIEKING)
(HEART BEATING)
Sinon: (PANTING)
ULTIMA RATIO HECATE TWO.
HECATE.
Player: (GRUNTS) YO, DYNE!
YOU SURE YOU GOT
THE RIGHT INFO?
ARE THEY COMIN', OR WHAT?
Dyne: THEY'RE COMIN',
ALL RIGHT.
I CHECKED THE ROUTE MYSELF,
SO RELAX.
I BET THEY'RE BUSY CLEARING
SOME BIG‐ASS MONSTER SPAWN.
THAT MEANS YOUR CUT'LL
BE BIGGER THIS TIME,
SO NO COMPLAINING.
Player: DUDE,
NO ONE'S COMPLAININ'!
BUT SINCE WE'RE
TALKIN' ABOUT IT,
AIN'T THESE THE SAME
JOKERS WE HIT LAST WEEK?
THEY COULDA WISED UP TO US
AND CHANGED THEIR ROUTE.
Dyne: ALL THAT SQUAD DOES
IS HUNT MONSTERS.
THEY DON'T CARE HOW MANY
TIMES THEY GET ATTACKED,
'CAUSE THEY'LL JUST MAKE UP
FOR IT ON THEIR NEXT HUNT.
FOR PLAYER‐HUNTER
SQUADS LIKE US,
THEY MAKE THE PERFECT TARGET.
THEY MOVE BY ALGORITHM,
JUST LIKE THE MONSTERS.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
THEY'RE CHUMPS.
Player #2:
DAMN STRAIGHT.
Dyne: AS FOR WEAPONS,
THEY'RE GEARED UP
WITH OPTICAL GUNS
FOR HUNTING MONSTERS.
BUT WE'VE GOT DEFENSE SHIELDS,
SO AS LONG AS THOSE'RE UP,
IT'S EASY PICKINGS.
Player 1: WELL, WHAT IF
THEY GOT SMART?
LIKE, WHAT IF THEY'RE
READY FOR US THIS TIME?
Dyne: WE HIT 'EM NOT
TOO LONG AGO, RIGHT?
I DOUBT THEY GOT THEIR HANDS ON
ENOUGH LIVE‐AMMO GUNS THAT FAST.
BY NOW, THEY MIGHT HAVE
ONE FIREARM FOR SUPPORT,
BUT THAT'S ABOUT IT.
AND BESIDES...
WE GOT THE BEST SNIPER
IN "GGO" WATCHIN' OUR BACKS.
WE'VE GOT ALL
OUR BASES COVERED.
RIGHT, SINON?
Sinon: YEP.
Dyne: (SIGHS)
Player #1: GUESS I CAN'T
ARGUE WITH THAT.
WITH A CRACK SHOT
LIKE SINON UP HERE,
THINGS'RE LOOKIN' GOO‐OOD!
Dyne: (CLEARING THROAT)
IT'S BETTER THAN GOOD.
Player #1: WELL, "IF"‐‐
IT'S A BIG "IF," BUT STILL.
IF SHE MISSED,
I'D BE COOL WITH THAT.
IT'LL TAKE THEM ABOUT A MINUTE
TO FIGURE OUT
WHERE THE SHOT CAME FROM.
WHILE THEY'RE DOIN' THAT,
I'LL BE IN POSITION.
I'LL HOSE 'EM DOWN
AND RAKE IN THE MON‐EY.
Dyne:
EASY, COWBOY.
Ginrou: HEYA, DOLLFACE.
I WAS WONDERIN'.
WHAT YOU DOIN' AFTER THIS?
I FOUND A GUN SHOP WITH
AN AWESOME INVENTORY.
MAYBE WE COULD GO GET SOME TEA
OR MAYBE DO SOMETHIN' ELSE!
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
(CHUCKLES)
Sinon: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN, GINROU.
BESIDES, THERE'S STUFF I
HAVE TO DO WHEN I LOG OUT.
Ginrou: AH, COME ON, DOLLFACE!
WHAT "STUFF"?!
WAIT. ARE YOU
STILL IN SCHOOL?
THAT'S KINDA HOT.
YOU GOT A REPORT DUE?!
Sinon: YEAH. RIGHT.
Player #2:
LAY OFF HER, GINROU.
DON'T PUT HER ON
THE SPOT LIKE THAT.
WE'RE WORKIN', SO DON'T
BRING UP THE REAL WORLD IN HERE.
Player #3: YEAH, MAN!
THIS AIN'T THE TIME OR PLACE
TO RE‐SPEC YOUR SOLO STATUS!
Ginrou: LIKE YOU GUYS CAN TALK!
WHEN'S THE LAST TIME
EITHER OF YOU GOT LUCKY?!
Player #3: (LAUGHING)
LAST NIGHT! WITH YOUR SISTER!
Sinon: (SIGHS)
Dyne: KNOCK IT OFF.
STAY SHARP.
Player #4: GOT 'EM.
Dyne: 'BOUT TIME
THEY SHOWED UP TO THE PARTY.
YUP. IT'S THEM.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
THAT'S ONE MORE
THAN LAST WEEK.
WE GOT FOUR OPTICAL BLASTERS
IN THE FRONT.
I SEE ONE LARGE CALIBER
LASER RIFLE.
NOT A PROBLEM.
AND A GUY WITH A MINIMI.
HE GOES DOWN FIRST.
THE NEW GUY IN THE BACK,
HE'S GOT A CLOAK ON.
CAN'T SEE WHAT HE'S CARRYING.
Ginrou: HE'S WEARIN' A CLOAK?!
Dyne: YEAH.
Ginrou: MAYBE IT'S HIM,
THAT DEATH GUN GUY
EVERYONE'S TALKIN' ABOUT!
Dyne: HUH. NO WAY!
WHAT, YOU BELIEVE IN
FAIRY TALES NOW?
HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S
STRENGTH‐BUILD.
PROBABLY JUST A COURIER, THOUGH.
IF ANYTHING, I BET HE'S
CARRYING THE SQUAD'S AMMO,
ENERGY PACKS AND DROPS.
EH, WE CAN IGNORE HIM.
Sinon: I'M GETTING A BAD VIBE
FROM THE GUY IN BACK.
I THINK WE SHOULD TAKE HIM OUT
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE.
Dyne: NO WAY. HE'S NOT
CARRYING ANY WEAPONS.
Sinon: MAYBE HE IS.
MAYBE HE ISN'T.
HE'S AN UNKNOWN,
SO HE'S A RISK.
Dyne: I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE SAYIN',
BUT THERE'S ALSO A MINIMI
OUT THERE, AND THAT'S A PROBLEM.
IF HE STARTS LIGHTING US UP
AND THOSE BLASTERS MOVE IN,
IT'S GONNA GET UGLY.
Sinon: UNDERSTOOD. I'LL DROP
THE GUY WITH THE MINIMI FIRST,
BUT MY SECOND BULLET'S
GOT MR. CLOAK'S NAME ON IT.
Player #4: HATE TO INTERRUPT YOU
GUYS, BUT THEY'RE CLOSING ON US.
THEY'RE AT TWENTY‐FIVE
HUNDRED METERS.
Dyne: ALL RIGHT.
'WE'RE GONNA STICK WITH
THE ORIGINAL PLAN
AND WAIT FOR 'EM
IN THE SHADOW OF THAT BUILDING.
SINON, CALL OUT
IF THE SITUATION CHANGES.
WAIT FOR MY ORDER TO FIRE.
Sinon: ROGER.
Dyne: ALL RIGHT, MOVE OUT.
Dyne: I'M IN POSITION.
Sinon: ROGER. TARGETS
HAVEN'T CHANGED THEIR COURSE,
OR THEIR SPEED.
THEY'RE FOUR HUNDRED
METERS FROM YOU,
FIFTEEN HUNDRED FROM ME.
Dyne: PRETTY FAR.
CAN YOU MAKE THE SHOT?
Sinon: NO SWEAT.
Dyne: OKAY, THEN.
FIRE WHEN READY.
I'M COUNTING ON YOU, SINON.
Sinon: ROGER.
THIS PRESSURE...
THIS ANXIETY...
THIS FEAR.
FIFTEEN HUNDRED METERS,
THAT'S NOTHING,
LIKE TOSSING A WAD OF PAPER
INTO A TRASH CAN.
NO WAY.
THIS IS NOTHING LIKE
HOW IT FELT THAT DAY.
(HEART BEATING)
NEXT.
(INHALES)
(EXHALES)
CAN'T CHANGE POSITION.
I CLEARED THE FIRST TARGET,
BUT I COULDN'T POP
THE SECOND ONE.
Dyne: ROGER THAT.
SIT TIGHT UP THERE, YOU HEAR?
GO, GO, GO!
(GASPS)
HE'S GOT A...MINIGUN!
THEY'RE NOT LATE 'CAUSE
THEIR HUNT WAS RUNNING LONG.
THEY'RE MOVING SLOW
IN THE FIELD,
'CAUSE THE WEIGHT
OF THAT MINIGUN'S
GOT A MOVEMENT PENALTY!
Ginrou: (LAUGHING)
HMM.
Ginrou: SCORE!
HA! I KNEW IT.
THIS OP'S GONNA BE A CAKEWALK.
Sinon: (GASPS)
WHAT WAS THAT?
IF HE CAN SMILE
IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIREFIGHT,
HE MUST BE PRETTY BRAVE...
OR CRAZY.
Sinon: EITHER WAY, HE'S MINE!
Dyne: DUCK!
CRAP!
DON'T LET HIM GET CLOSER! FIRE!
Player #3:
Y‐YEAH, ROGER THAT!
(BULLETS WHIZZING)
Dyne: GOTTA FIND SOME COVER.
BUT WHERE?
WHERE, DAMN IT. WHERE?!
S‐SINON?
Player #3: SINON!
ARE YOU HIT?
Dyne: BASTARDS.
(GROWLS)
THEY TEAMED UP WITH
A FREAKIN' BODYGUARD!
Sinon: BODYGUARD?
Dyne: IT'S THAT GUY
WITH THE MINIGUN.
HE'S A MACHO PRICK,
CALLS HIMSELF BEHEMOTH.
Sinon: WELL, WE CAN'T
KEEP SITTING HERE,
'CAUSE THEY'RE GONNA
WIPE US OUT!
THAT MINIGUN'S ONLY GOT
SO MUCH AMMO TO FIRE.
IF WE ATTACK HIM AT ONCE,
HE'LL PANIC
AND BURN THROUGH
THE REST OF IT.
JIN AND MISO,
YOU TAKE THE LEFT FLANK.
DYNE AND I'LL
COME IN FROM THE RIGHT.
ARASHI, YOU STAY HERE
AND COVER US.
Dyne: THAT'S CRAZY.
Dyne: WHAT ABOUT
THE THREE GUYS OUT THERE
CARRYING THE BLASTERS?
EVEN IF WE RUSH 'EM,
OUR DEFENSE SHIELDS
AREN'T ENOUGH!
Sinon: RIGHT, BUT THEIR
BLASTERS CAN'T FIRE
AS FAST AS A LIVE‐AMMO GUN.
WE CAN JUST DODGE 'EM!
Dyne: SCREW THAT! IF WE GO
CHARGING OUT THERE,
THAT MINIGUN'LL
TURN US INTO CONFETTI!
(DEEP BREATH)
SORRY, BUT WE'RE PACKIN' IT IN.
IT'S BETTER IF WE
LOGGED OUT RIGHT NOW.
AT LEAST WE'LL BE
ABLE TO GET AWAY.
Sinon: YOU DON'T GET AWAY
FROM THINGS BY LOGGING OUT.
Dyne: ARE YOU NUTS?! THIS IS
A GAME, FOR CHRIST SAKES!
THINK ABOUT IT.
EVEN IF WE CHARGED 'EM,
WE'D JUST DIE!
‐ Sinon: THEN DIE!
‐ Dyne: (GASPS)
Sinon: IT IS A GAME, SO YOU
CAN AT LEAST HAVE THE BALLS
TO FACE DEATH HERE
INSTEAD OF WHININ'!
Sinon: WE CAN DO THIS.
IF YOU CAN DISTRACT
THE MINIGUN FOR THREE SECONDS,
I CAN TAKE HIM OUT.
Player #3: O‐OKAY.
Sinon: GOOD.
THEN WE'LL SPLIT UP
AND ATTACK HIM
FROM BOTH SIDES. GOT IT?
‐ Player #2: GOT IT!
‐ Player #3: GOT IT!
Sinon: GO!
DYNE! COVER ME!
Dyne: HOW YOU LIKE THAT, PUNK?!
(SCREAMING)
SCREW YOU!
‐ Opponent: YES.
‐ Opponent #2: (LAUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
Sinon: NICE GOING! NOW...
I'VE GOTTA FIGURE OUT HOW TO
GET INTO BEHEMOTH'S BLIND SPOT.
I'D BETTER MOVE FAST.
OR HE'S GONNA GET
A BEAD ON MY LOCATION.
BULLETS ARE FLYIN', AND HE'S GOT
THE GUTS TO SMILE LIKE THAT.
MAYBE I WILL,
TOO, WHEN I KILL HIM.
(GASPS)
Behemoth: (LAUGHING)
Sinon: YOU'RE DEAD.
(SHUDDERS)
DAMN IT.
I GOTTA GET STRONGER.
Silica: (SCREAMS)
Leafa: SILICA!
Silica: HA HA! I'VE GOT
A NEW TRICK UP MY SLEEVE!
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
L‐LEAFA! HELP ME!
Leafa: I'M COMIN'!
LISBETH!
Leafa: YAY!
Lisbeth: (CHUCKLES)
LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT.
Silica: PLEASE TELL ME
THAT'S THE LAST OF IT.
Lisbeth: HMM.
I THINK I PRETTY MUCH
GOT EVERYTHING I NEED NOW.
Leafa: YOU WANNA
KEEP GOING SOME MORE?
YOU ALWAYS HOOK US UP AT
YOUR SHOP, SO IF YOU NEED MORE,
WE DON'T MIND HELPING.
Lisbeth: THANKS, GUYS.
ALTHOUGH...
HMM. WE SORTA PICKED
THIS PLACE CLEAN, DIDN'T WE?
Leafa: LET'S TAKE A BREAK
AND LET 'EM RESPAWN.
Silica: OKAY.
THEY'RE SO INTO EACH OTHER.
Lisbeth: IT'S NOT FAIR,
DAMN IT.
Leafa: NOW, NOW...!
Lisbeth: UCH. DOESN'T MATTER
IF THEY'RE AT SCHOOL OR HERE,
THEY CAN'T KEEP THEIR HANDS
OFF EACH OTHER!
Leafa: YOU MEAN THEY'RE
LIKE THIS AT SCHOOL, TOO?
Silica:
ALL DAY, EVERY DAY.
Leafa:
(SIGHS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Kirito:
ASUNA...
THERE'S SOMETHING IMPORTANT
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO TELL YOU.