Death Gun: WHETHER YOU'RE
A FAKE USING HIS NAME
OR THE REAL GUY,
SOMEDAY I'LL KILL YOU.
Kirito: THE FIRST TIME
DEATH GUN SHOWED UP
WAS AFTER THE SECOND
BULLET OF BULLETS,
AND BOTH
OF THE MURDERS HE COMMITTED
HAPPENED IN FRONT
OF WITNESSES.
HE'S BEEN STAYING
UNDER THE RADAR
SINCE THE LAST KILLING,
PROBABLY LEVELING UP
AS MUCH AS HE CAN.
I DON'T SEE ANYONE REGISTERED
AS DEATH GUN HERE,
BUT IF HE WANTS
TO STAGE ANOTHER MURDER,
B.o.B.'s PERFECT.
HE'LL BE HERE.
I KNOW IT.
I GOTTA FIND OUT THE NAME
OF DEATH GUN'S AVATAR
AND STOP HIM.
Kirito: HEY.
HEY, SINON.
HELLO. ANYONE HOME?
‐ COME O‐‐
‐ Sinon: SHUT UP.
I THOUGHT I MADE IT CLEAR
I WAS DONE TALKING.
GOD, WHAT ELSE
DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
Kirito: N‐NOTHING.
BUT NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
MAYBE WE COULD SWAP SOME INFO
BEFORE THIS STARTS.
I MEAN...
LIKE, YOU KNOW,
FOR OLD TIMES' SAKE.
Sinon: (SIGHS)
FINE. WHATEVER.
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: I'LL DO IT,
EVEN THOUGH I'M THE ONE WHO'S
GONNA BE GIVING ALL THE INFO.
Kirito: BUT I GOT STUFF
TO SHARE, TOO.
IT'S NOT A LOT, BUT STILL...
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Interviewer:
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
YOU THINK YOU GOT A SHOT
THIS TIME?
Dyne: BY THE TIME HE SEES ME,
IT'LL BE TOO LATE.
Kirito: THIS IS CRAZY.
Sinon: YEAH. THE FINAL
IS LIKE ONE BIG PARTY.
Kirito: YEAH. (CHUCKLES)
Merchant: ...PICKING A WINNER IS
GONNA BE TOUGHER THAN EVER!
FOR ONLY 1,000 CREDS,
I CAN HOOK YOU UP
WITH TOP‐SECRET INFO
ON ALL THE TOP PLAYERS.
Player: HERE GOES.
ALL ON YAMIKAZE.
Player 2: I WONDER
WHAT HUUKA'S ODDS ARE.
Player 3: COME ON. DYNE?
SURE, HE'S GOT GOOD GEAR
AND SOLID SKILLS,
BUT THAT DUDE'S
OLDER THAN HELL, YOU KNOW.
AT BEST,
HE'D COME IN 15th TODAY.
IF YOU WANT TO GO WITH
A LONG SHOT, GO WITH RICHIE.
HMM?
Dyne: (CHUCKLES)
SO YOU THINK
I'M TOO OLD TO GET IT ON?
Player 3:
NO, I WAS JUST SAYING...
Dyne: THIS OLD DOG'S
GOT SOME NEW TRICKS.
Player 4: HEY, LOOK.
I‐IT'S KIRITO.
Player 5: SHE HACKS UP PEOPLE
GOOD WITH THAT PHOTON SWORD.
Player 6: OH,
A HOT BERSERKER WITH A BLADE.
Player 5:
SINON'S MORE MY TYPE, BROTHER.
Player 4: I WOULDN'T MIND
GETTING A BULLET FROM SINON.
Player 5: ROGER THAT.
Player 6: HEH.
I'D RATHER GET SLASHED.
Player 4: THEN GO PLAY "A. L. O."
WITH THE FAERIES.
Kirito: (GASPS)
OH, SORRY.
Players:
(GASPS) YOU'RE KIRITO!
S‐SORRY!
(GASPS)
(SHUDDERING)
Kirito: HEY, GUYS...
HOPE Y'ALL ROOT FOR ME.
Players: (GASP)
Player 7: Y‐YOU GOT IT.
GOOD LUCK OUT THERE.
Player 8:
I BET MY LIFE SAVINGS ON YOU.
Kirito: (LAUGHS)
Sinon: OH, GOD.
QUIT MESSING WITH THEM.
Kirito: OKAY. (CLEARS THROAT)
SO 30 PLAYERS GET DROPPED
RANDOMLY ACROSS THE SAME MAP,
AND THEN‐‐(GASPS)
AND THEN YOU GO AROUND
SHOOTING WHOEVER YOU FIND,
AND THE WINNER'S
THE LAST ONE STANDING?
Sinon: OH, MAN. KNEW IT.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE ME EXPLAIN
THE WHOLE DAMN THING
TO YOU AFTER ALL.
DON'T YOU HAVE E‐MAIL?
THE ADMINS SENT THE RULES OUT,
SO IT SHOULD BE SITTING
IN YOUR IN‐BOX.
Kirito: YEAH, I DID
SCAN THROUGH IT, BUT...
IT'S LIKE I WANTED
TO MAKE SURE I UNDERSTOOD.
THERE WAS A LOT OF INFO
TO ABSORB.
Sinon: (SCOFFS) "ABSORB."
BASICALLY YOU PRETTY MUCH
GOT THE GIST OF IT.
THIS THING'S A BATTLE ROYALE
BETWEEN 30 PLAYERS
ON THE SAME MAP.
START POINTS ARE RANDOM,
AND PLAYERS ARE DROPPED
ABOUT 1,000 METERS
AWAY FROM EACH OTHER.
Kirito: WHOA. 1,000.
THAT'S GOTTA BE
ONE INSANELY HUGE MAP.
Sinon: HONESTLY, YOU DIDN'T
READ THE E‐MAIL, DID YOU?
(SIGHS)
IT'S A MULTISTAGE ARENA
10 KILOMETERS IN DIAMETER.
IT'S GOT MOUNTAINS,
FORESTS, AND DESERTS.
THE START TIME'S AFTERNOON,
SO THERE'S NO ADVANTAGE
OR DISADVANTAGE
IN TERMS OF GEAR OR SKILLS.
Kirito: HOW CAN YOU FIND ANYONE
IN A FIELD THAT BIG?
Sinon:
THAT MAKES IT CHALLENGING.
IT'S A GAME WITH GUNFIGHTS,
REMEMBER?
ANYWAY, PLAYERS GET AN ITEM
TO TRACK OTHER PLAYERS.
IT'S CALLED A SATELLITE
SCAN TERMINAL.
Kirito: THERE'S A SATELLITE?
LIKE A SPY DRONE OR SOMETHING?
Sinon: YEP.
IT WORKS JUST LIKE IN REAL LIFE.
IT PASSES OVERHEAD
EVERY 15 MINUTES.
IT SCANS THE ARENA
AND THEN TRANSMITS
THE COORDINATES
OF ALL THE PLAYERS
DIRECTLY TO YOUR TERMINAL.
NEAT, HUH?
Kirito: HMM.
SO BASICALLY YOU CAN ONLY HIDE
IN ONE SPOT FOR 15 MINUTES.
Sinon: YOU CATCH ON QUICK.
Kirito: BUT THEN DOESN'T
ALL THAT MOVING AROUND
PUT A SNIPER
AT A DISADVANTAGE?
Sinon: 15 MINUTES
IS MORE THAN ENOUGH TIME
FOR A SNIPER TO DO THEIR JOB.
I FIRE. I KILL MY TARGET.
I MOVE ON.
Kirito: UH, YEAH, I GUESS.
Sinon: SO WE GOOD HERE? GREAT.
NEXT TIME WE SEE EACH OTHER...
‐ Kirito: NO! WAIT!
‐ Sinon: YOU CAN BET YOUR ASS‐‐
‐ Kirito: HOLD ON!
‐ (DRINK SPILLS)
Sinon: IS THERE SOMETHING ELSE?
Kirito: UH‐HUH.
IT'S WHAT I REALLY
WANT TO TALK ABOUT.
Sinon: (SIGHS)
MM.
Kirito: HANG ON.
COULD YOU TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS LIST REAL QUICK?
OUT OF ALL
THE B. o. B. CONTESTANTS,
ARE THERE ANY FIRST‐TIMERS
WHOSE NAMES YOU DON'T RECOGNIZE?
Sinon: OKAY, THAT'S WEIRD.
Kirito: PLEASE,
JUST LOOK AT IT, AND TELL ME.
IT'S IMPORTANT.
Sinon: WELL, IF THAT'S
ALL YOU WANT TO KNOW,
I GUESS IT'S COOL.
THE FIRST‐TIMERS I DON'T KNOW,
BESIDES A CERTAIN LOSER
WITH A PHOTON SWORD,
ARE THREE NAMES.
Kirito: THAT'S GREAT. WHO?
POINT 'EM OUT.
Sinon: JUSHI X, PALE RIDER,
AND THIS GUY,
STERBEN?
Kirito: (THINKING)
IS ONE OF THEM DEATH GUN?
Sinon: YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT,
OR ARE YOU
GONNA KEEP ME IN THE DARK?
Kirito: UH...
Sinon: GETTING READY
TO BLOW A FUSE OVER HERE.
Kirito: UH...
Sinon: SPEAK UP.
I SWEAR, IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO MAKE ME MESS UP TODAY
BY PISSING ME OFF, I'M GONNA...
Kirito: NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
IT'S JUST THAT...
Sinon: DOES IT
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH WHY YOU WERE
ACTING WEIRD YESTERDAY,
YOU KNOW, AFTER THE PRELIMS?
Kirito: UH‐HUH. IT DOES.
YESTERDAY, THIS PERSON
I ONCE PLAYED AGAINST
IN ANOTHER V.R.M.M.O.
CAME UP TO ME.
I'M PRETTY SURE ONE OF THE NAMES
YOU POINTED OUT IS HIM.
Sinon: IS HE A FRIEND OF YOURS?
Kirito: NO, AN ENEMY.
I CAN'T REMEMBER
HIS NAME, THOUGH,
AND I THINK WE TRIED
TO KILL EACH OTHER.
Sinon: KILL EACH OTHER?
FOR REAL?
WAS IT LIKE AN ARGUMENT
WITH SOMEONE IN YOUR PARTY,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
Kirito: NO WAY.
IT WASN'T THAT.
YOU DON'T KILL SOMEONE
OVER AN ARGUMENT.
HIM AND HIS GROUP
DID HORRIBLE THINGS,
THINGS LIKE MURDER.
THEY WERE TOO FAR GONE,
AND THE ONLY WAY
TO STOP THEM WAS BY FORCE.
I DON'T REGRET WHAT I DID,
BUT STILL, I'VE AVOIDED
TAKING RESPONSIBILITY FOR IT.
I FORCED MYSELF TO FORGET
IT EVEN HAPPENED.
FOR ME,
THERE'S NO MORE RUNNING AWAY,
AND THIS TIME, I HAVE TO FACE
WHAT I DID HEAD‐ON.
SORRY TO EMOTE LIKE THAT.
JUST FORGET IT.
Sinon: DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
STILL PULL THE TRIGGER, THOUGH?
Kirito: (GASPS)
COULD YOU SHOOT A PLAYER IN HERE
IF YOU KNEW, IN THE REAL WORLD,
THAT PLAYER WOULD DIE FROM IT?
AND WHAT IF YOU
HAD TO KILL THAT PLAYER,
'CAUSE IF YOU DIDN'T, YOU OR
SOMEONE YOU LOVE WOULD DIE?
IF YOU HAD THAT POWER,
COULD YOU STILL
PULL THAT TRIGGER?
Sinon: KIRITO...
WHAT'S THE NAME OF THE GAME
YOU MET THIS GUY IN?
SORRY. NEVER MIND.
THAT'S PERSONAL.
Kirito: NO, THAT'S OKAY.
Sinon: KIRITO...
I...
Kirito: SINON?
Sinon: WE SHOULD START HEADING
OVER TO THE WAITING DOME NOW.
WE HAVE TO CHECK OUR GEAR
AND GET OURSELVES
PSYCHED UP FOR THIS BATTLE.
Kirito: YEAH, SURE.
LEAD THE WAY.
Sinon: I GET YOU'VE GOT
YOUR REASONS FOR BEING HERE,
JUST LIKE ME.
BUT IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT PROMISE YOU MADE.
I GOTTA PAY YOU BACK
FOR WHAT HAPPENED
IN YESTERDAY'S FINAL. GOT IT?
YOU OWE ME A FIGHT,
SO YOU BETTER STAY ALIVE.
Kirito: ROGER THAT.
I PROMISE I'LL SURVIVE
AND GIVE YOU THE FIGHT YOU WANT.
Sinon: THANKS.
Emcee: IF YOU'RE
A BATTLE JUNKIE
WHO LOVES THE SMELL
OF GUN OIL AND GUN SMOKE,
THEN GET READY!
PLACE YOUR BETS,
'CAUSE WE'RE ABOUT TO START!
Merchant: (CHUCKLES)
Emcee: NOW ARE
YOU GUYS READY TO FIND OUT
WHO'S THE STRONGEST PLAYER
IN "GUN GALE ONLINE,"
THE HARDEST GAME IN TOWN?
Crowd: (CHEERING, YELLING)
Emcee: AS USUAL, MMO STREAM
WILL BE BROADCASTING THE BATTLE
LIVE AND UNCENSORED!
ALL RIGHT, HELP ME OUT
WITH THE COUNTDOWN, GUYS.
Crowd: 10, 9, 8,
7, 6, 5,
4, 3, 2,
1!
Emcee: THE THIRD
BULLET OF BULLETS HAS BEGUN!
Crowd: (CHEERING)
(GUNFIRE)
Player 9: (GASPS)
Dyne: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: (SCOFFS)
HMM?
BINGO.
Crowd: (CHEERING)
‐ Player 4: ALL RIGHT.
‐ Player 5: YEAH, YOU GO, GIRL.
Sinon: 21 SURVIVORS
LEFT IN PLAY.
LOOKS LIKE DYNE'S ON THE RUN.
RICHIE'S GOT
A HEAVY MACHINE GUN,
SO HE'LL SIT TIGHT.
HE LIKES HIS PREY COMING TO HIM.
I'LL GO AFTER DYNE
AND PALE RIDER.
WONDER HOW HE'S DOING OUT THERE.
AH, WHAT THE HELL DO I CARE?
Dyne: (PANTING)
DAMN. THIS GUY'S
FREAKING PERSISTENT.
EH?
HEH.
COME ON. I GOT A MAG FULL
OF ROUNDS WITH YOUR NAME ON 'EM.
Sinon: YOU FORGOT
TO CHECK YOUR SIX AGAIN, DYNE.
SEE YOU LATER.
(GASPS)
WHO'S THERE?
Kirito: SHH.
KEEP IT DOWN.
I NEED A FAVOR.
Sinon: ARE YOU KIDDING?
IT'S TOO LATE
FOR ANY MORE FAVORS.
ONE OF US DIES RIGHT NOW.
Kirito: STOP IT.
I DON'T WANT THOSE GUYS
TO KNOW WE'RE HERE.
Sinon: WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
Kirito: I WANT TO WATCH
WHAT HAPPENS ON THAT BRIDGE,
SO DON'T SHOOT, OKAY?
Sinon: OKAY. THEN WHAT?
Kirito: THAT DEPENDS,
BUT I'M NOT HERE FOR YOU.
I'LL LEAVE AFTER, PROMISE.
Sinon: THE MINUTE
YOU TURN YOUR BACK,
I'LL BLOW YOU AWAY.
Kirito: IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
THEN FINE, BUT FOR NOW,
JUST STAY QUIET.
Sinon: ALL RIGHT,
BUT AFTER THEY'RE DONE
DOWN THERE, IT'S YOU AND ME.
Kirito: OKAY.
Sinon: YOUR STEALTH SKILLS
ARE PRETTY PATHETIC.
I'M NOT LETTING HIM
LEAVE THE AREA ALIVE.
IF HE MAKES A MOVE,
I'M TAKING THE SHOT.
Kirito: HE'S ALL YOURS.
WAIT. COMPANY.
Dyne: EH? SON OF A...
(CHUCKLES)
DAMN.
Sinon: WHOA. HE'S FAST.
HE BOOSTED
HIS THREE‐DIMENSIONAL MOBILITY
BY CARRYING LIGHTER GEAR.
HIS ACROBATIC SKILLS
ARE THROUGH THE ROOF.
Dyne: BASTARD.
(GROANS)
(GUNSHOT)
NO.
Sinon: IF ONLY HE HAD TIME
TO SWITCH MAGS,
HE COULD HAVE SHOT FROM THE HIP
AND KILLED HIM EASY.
Kirito: THAT PALE GUY,
HE'S QUICK AND POWERFUL.
MAYBE HE'S THE ONE
IN THE CLOAK.
AN ENEMY. I THINK WE TRIED
TO KILL EACH OTHER ONCE BEFORE.
Sinon: I'M TAKING HIM OUT.
Kirito: OKAY,
BUT IT WON'T BE EASY
IF HE'S WHO I THINK.
Sinon: OH, PLEASE.
HE CAN'T DODGE MY BULLET
AT THIS RANGE.
Both: (GASP)
(RIVER RUSHING)
Sinon: DID YOU HEAR A GUNSHOT?
Kirito: THERE WASN'T ONE.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
Sinon: TWO POSSIBILITIES.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN A LASER RIFLE
WITH A MUFFLED BLAST
OR MAYBE A LIVE‐AMMO GUN
WITH A SILENCER.
EITHER WAY,
IT WASN'T A KILL SHOT,
SO WHY ISN'T HE MOVING?
Kirito: I THINK THE SHOT
CAME FROM THE FOREST.
Sinon: UH‐UH. HE WAS SNIPED
FROM FURTHER AWAY THAN THAT.
I DID A SCAN OF THE MAP
NOT TOO LONG AGO.
THERE'S NO ONE
WITHIN ONE KILOMETER OF HERE.
AND NOW THAT WE'RE
ON THE SUBJECT,
YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHERE YOU CAME FROM?
Kirito: UH, I WAS CHASING
AFTER THAT PALE RIDER GUY.
HANG ON.
OH, NO WAY.
Sinon: WHAT'S UP?
Kirito: WHEN THE SATELLITE
WAS SCANNING THE AREA,
I WAS SWIMMING IN THAT RIVER.
I GUESS MY LOCATION
DIDN'T REGISTER ON THE MAP
'CAUSE I WAS UNDERWATER.
Sinon: WITH ALL THAT GEAR,
YOU SHOULD HAVE DROWNED.
Kirito: NAH. I TOOK IT ALL OFF
BEFORE I DOVE IN,
STUCK IT IN MY ITEM STORAGE.
Sinon: (SIGHS)
I NEVER KNEW
WE COULD USE THE RIVER
FOR COVER FROM THE SATELLITE.
THANKS FOR THE TIP.
I'LL KEEP IT IN MIND.
Kirito: SINON,
CHECK OUT HIS SHOULDER.
THERE'S A WEIRD LIGHT THERE.
Sinon: A STUN BULLET.
Kirito: (GASPS)
HOW LONG'S HE BEEN THERE?
Sinon: HE'S GOT
A SILENT ASSASSIN.
Kirito: IS THAT
WHAT HIS RIFLE'S CALLED?
Sinon: YEAH.
IT'S A HIGH‐END SNIPER RIFLE
THAT'S GOT
A BAD‐ASS SILENCER ON IT.
I HEARD RUMORS
ABOUT THERE BEING ONE IN "GGO,"
BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN IT BEFORE.
IF HE CAN HANDLE THAT GUN,
HE MUST BE SOME PLAYER.
Kirito: (GASPS)
Sinon: WHY WOULD HE
USE HIS HANDGUN
TO FINISH HIM OFF?
Kirito: SINON, SHOOT.
Sinon: HUH? WHICH ONE?
Kirito: IT'S THE GUY
IN THE CLOAK.
THERE'S NO TIME! SHOOT HIM!
HURRY!
DON'T LET HIM FIRE THAT GUN!