Kirito: HUH. THERE'S NO ONE
ANYWHERE NEAR US.
DEATH GUN AND SINON
AREN'T ON THE MAP,
BUT COUNTING THEM,
THERE'S SIX PLAYERS LEFT.
HUH?
THEY TOOK EACH OTHER OUT.
THAT LEAVES FOUR.
(GASPS)
30 PLAYERS STARTED.
24 ARE OUT, SO THAT LEAVES SIX.
ME AND YAMIKAZE
AND SINON AND DEATH GUN,
THAT'S 28,
AND PALE RIDER MAKES IT 29.
WE'RE SHORT A PLAYER.
DID DEATH GUN
MURDER SOMEONE ELSE
AFTER HE GOT PALE RIDER?
NO. HIS PARTNER'S BEEN WAITING
AT SINON'S FOR HIS CUE.
HE CAN'T BE TWO PLACES AT ONCE.
UNLESS...
THERE'S ANOTHER ANGLE
TO THIS I'M MISSING.
(ROCKS SLIDE)
Sinon: (GASPS)
WELL, WHAT'D YOU FIND?
Kirito: THERE'S FIVE OF US LEFT,
YOU, ME, YAMIKAZE‐‐
I DIDN'T SEE DEATH GUN, THOUGH.
AND THERE'S ANOTHER PLAYER
OUT THERE SOMEWHERE.
THE SCAN DIDN'T PICK HIM UP,
SO THEY MIGHT BE HIDING
IN A CAVE LIKE US.
Sinon: THAT'S IT, JUST US FIVE?
WELL, IT'S BEEN AN HOUR
AND 45 MINUTES ALREADY.
SEEING AS HOW THE LAST B.o.B.
ENDED IN ABOUT TWO HOURS,
THIS ONE'S RIGHT ON SCHEDULE.
HEH. I'M SURPRISED NO ONE'S
CHUCKED A GRENADE IN HERE YET.
Kirito: YEAH. MAYBE WE'VE GOT
DEATH GUN TO THANK FOR THAT.
COULD BE
WHILE HE'S LOOKING FOR US,
HE'S WHITTLING DOWN
THE COMPETITION
WITH THAT RIFLE OF HIS.
Sinon: IF YOU'RE RIGHT,
THEN HE'S A SHOO‐IN
FOR THE MAX‐KILLS AWARD.
WHATEVER.
WE SHOULD WORRY ABOUT YAMIKAZE.
YOU WERE PROBABLY THE ONLY ONE
WHO SHOWED UP ON HIS TERMINAL,
SO WE BETTER GET READY,
'CAUSE HE'LL BE COMING FOR YOU.
Kirito: HE ANY GOOD?
Sinon: HE WAS RUNNER‐UP
IN THE LAST B. o. B.
HE'S YOUR TYPICAL
FULL‐ON AGI TYPE.
THEY CALL HIM THE RUN‐GUN DEMON
OR SOMETHING.
Kirito: UH, RUN WHAT?
Sinon: RUN AND GUN.
YOU RUN, SHOOT, RUN.
IT'S A STYLE OF COMBAT.
HIS MAIN WEAPON'S
A CALICO M900A,
AN ULTRALIGHT SUBMACHINE GUN.
YAMIKAZE COULDN'T COMPETE
WITH ZXE‐D's RARE GUN AND ARMOR
IN THE LAST TOURNEY,
BUT EVEN THOUGH HE DIDN'T WIN,
SOME PEOPLE SAY
HE'S THE BETTER PLAYER.
Kirito: WHOA.
HE'S REALLY THAT GOOD?
LIKE THE BEST PLAYER
ON JAPAN'S "GGO" SERVER GOOD?
Sinon: YEAH, HE IS,
AND HE MIGHT BE
OUR ACE IN THE HOLE, TOO.
IF YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT DEATH GUN,
THEN I'M THE ONLY ONE
HE'S READY TO KILL.
YOU KNOW, 'CAUSE HIS PARTNER'S
WAITING BACK AT MY APARTMENT
RIGHT NOW.
SEE, I FIGURE
THAT IF THAT'S THE CASE,
YAMIKAZE'S NOT IN ANY
REAL DANGER OF GETTING KILLED.
THIS IS GONNA SOUND COLD,
BUT I WAS THINKING HE WOULD MAKE
THE PERFECT DECOY FOR US.
WHEN DEATH GUN SHOOTS YAMIKAZE,
WE'LL KNOW WHERE HE IS.
IN A WAY, WE GOT TWO DECOYS,
HIM IN HERE AND ME I. R. L.
Kirito:
YOU'RE PRETTY BRAVE, SINON.
Sinon: HUH?
NOT EVEN. I'M TRYING
NOT TO THINK ABOUT IT,
TRYING TO AVOID WHAT SCARES ME,
LIKE I ALWAYS DO.
ANYWAY, YOU THINK IT'LL WORK?
Kirito: YEAH. I MEAN,
IT SOUNDS PRETTY GOOD.
ALTHOUGH THERE'S
STILL ONE THING
THAT BOTHERS ME.
JUST NOW, WHEN I ADDED UP
THE PLAYERS WHO WERE LEFT
AND WHO WERE DONE,
I COULD ONLY COME UP WITH 28.
PALE RIDER'S 29,
BUT STILL, WE'RE SHORT ONE.
Sinon: NO WAY.
COULD DEATH GUN
HAVE KILLED SOMEONE ELSE
AFTER HE TRIED FOR ME?
HOW'S THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
I MEAN, HIS NUMBER TWO'S
SUPPOSED BE WAITING
AT MY PLACE NOW.
Kirito: RIGHT.
THAT'S HOW I FIGURED IT, TOO,
BUT NOW I'M THINKING
SOMETHING ELSE IS GOING ON.
BETWEEN THE TIME DEATH GUN
SHOT PALE RIDER
AND WHEN HE TRIED FOR YOU,
ONLY 30 MINUTES HAD GONE BY,
SO BASED ON MY THEORY,
PALE RIDER'S APARTMENT
WOULD HAVE TO BE
NO MORE THAN 30 MINUTES
AWAY FROM YOUR PLACE.
THAT'S KIND OF CONVENIENT,
DON'T YOU THINK?
Sinon: I GUESS,
BUT WHAT OTHER EXPLANATION
IS THERE FOR IT?
Kirito: MAYBE DEATH GUN ISN'T
WORKING WITH JUST THE ONE GUY.
LIKE MAYBE HE'S GOT
A FEW MORE PARTNERS.
IF HE DOES, THEN IT'D BE
POSSIBLE TO KILL ONE PLAYER
WHILE STILL HAVING SOMEONE
AVAILABLE TO KILL YOU
AND ONE FOR YAMIKAZE.
HE COULD BE A TARGET NOW, TOO.
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T KNOW.
(GUNSHOT)
Yamikaze: (GROANS)
Sinon: (GASPS)
OH, MY GOD.
IF YOU'RE RIGHT AND THERE'S
MORE OF 'EM OUT THERE,
HOW MANY MORE
ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
Kirito: IF THEY'RE ALL
EX‐LAUGHING COFFIN,
AT LEAST 10, MAYBE MORE.
I DOUBT THEY'RE ALL
INVOLVED WITH THIS,
BUT WE CAN'T BE SURE
THERE'S ONLY ONE REAL‐WORLD
KILLER OUT THERE ANYMORE.
Sinon: THEY'RE CRAZY.
WHY ELSE WOULD THEY DO THIS
AFTER GETTING OUT
OF "S. A. O." ALIVE?
HOW COULD ANYONE STAY
A PLAYER‐KILLER AFTER THAT GAME?
Kirito:
FOR THE SAME REASON AS US.
WHY DO I KEEP BEING A SWORDSMAN
AND YOU A SNIPER?
(RIFLE RATTLES)
Sinon: I CALLED 'EM P. K.‐ERS,
BUT I TAKE IT BACK.
THERE ARE LOTS OF PEOPLE
WHO P. K. IN THIS GAME.
I USED TO RUN WITH A SQUAD
OF P. K.‐ERS MYSELF.
BUT AT THE END OF THE DAY,
P.K.‐ERS HAVE A CODE OF HONOR
THEY STICK TO.
THEY'RE NOT P. K.‐ERS.
THEY KILL PEOPLE WITH POISON
WHILE THEY'RE UNCONSCIOUS
LIKE A BUNCH OF COWARDS.
THERE'S NO HONOR IN MURDER.
THAT'S CHICKENSHIT, STRAIGHT UP,
AND WE CAN'T LET THEM
GET AWAY WITH IT.
Kirito: NO, WE CAN'T.
WE'VE GOT A CHANCE
TO STOP THESE PEOPLE,
AND WE'RE GONNA TAKE IT.
DEATH GUN'S GOING DOWN
ON THIS BATTLEFIELD.
IT'S OVER FOR HIM AND HIS PALS.
I'LL MAKE 'EM ALL PAY.
YEAH,
THIS IS HOW I MAKE AMENDS
FOR WHAT I DID,
FOR LOSING IT
IN THE CHAOS OF BATTLE,
FOR KILLING THOSE TWO PLAYERS
THAT NIGHT
AND THE OTHER ONE LATER ON.
THIS IS HOW I'LL GET CLOSURE.
I'LL PROTECT SINON,
TAKE OUT YAMIKAZE,
AND END DEATH GUN.
IT WON'T BE EASY,
BUT IT'S WHAT I HAVE TO DO.
Sinon: I'M GONNA
TAKE YAMIKAZE OUT.
I WON'T LET DEATH GUN KILL HIM.
Kirito: HUH?
Sinon: YAMIKAZE'S TOUGH.
I DOUBT EVEN YOU
COULD FINISH HIM WITH ONE HIT,
AND IF HE'S BUSY WITH YOU,
DEATH GUN'S SURE TO GO FOR HIM.
Kirito: THEN HOW ARE WE
GONNA DEAL WITH THAT?
Sinon: DID YOU FORGET WHAT I AM?
I'M A SNIPER.
I'LL HAVE EYES ON YOU
THE WHOLE TIME,
SO ONCE THEY MOVE ON YOU,
I'LL KNOW THEIR LOCATIONS.
I'LL HIT YAMIKAZE FIRST.
THEN I'LL GO FOR DEATH GUN.
Kirito: OKAY, THEN.
WE GO WITH YOUR PLAN.
ALL RIGHT.
I THINK THEY SHOULD BE
PRETTY CLOSE BY NOW.
I'M GONNA HOP ON THE BUGGY
AND HEAD OUT.
LEAVE THE CAVE RIGHT AFTER I DO,
AND GET SET UP
AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
Sinon:
GOOD LUCK OUT THERE, PARTNER.
(CHUCKLES)
(GASPS)
YAMIKAZE'S COMING FROM THE WEST,
SO IF A SHOT
COMES FROM THE EAST,
IT'LL PROBABLY BE DEATH GUN.
HE'S GOT THAT CLOAK,
SO WHEN HE SHOOTS,
HE'LL BE INVISIBLE.
IF HE HITS KIRITO IN THE HEART
OR HEAD, IT'S OVER.
BUT IF YOU CAN CUT
MY BULLET IN HALF,
YOU CAN DODGE HIS, RIGHT?
RIGHT, KIRITO?
MY FIRST PRIORITY
IS TAKING YAMIKAZE
OUT OF THE PICTURE.
IF I MISS, KIRITO WILL GET SHOT.
THEN DEATH GUN
WILL FIND ME AND KILL ME.
MY LIFE, MY REAL LIFE,
DEPENDS ON A SINGLE BULLET,
LIKE IT DID THAT DAY.
PLEASE, HECATE.
I'M WEAK,
AND I NEED YOUR STRENGTH,
THE STRENGTH
TO STAND UP FOR MYSELF
AND MOVE ON.
Kirito: (SIGHS)
SOUTHWEST.
THAT'S YAMIKAZE.
DON'T WORRY. SINON'S GOT HIM.
(HEART BEATING)
Sinon: WHOA.
Yamikaze: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: WHAT DO I DO?
I COULD TRY
TO SHOOT IN FRONT OF HIM
OR SHOOT AT HIS FEET,
HOPE HE PANICS,
AND THEN TAKE HIM OUT.
NO. ONCE HE'S
GOT KIRITO IN RANGE,
HE'LL STOP TO STEADY HIS AIM.
I HAVE TO WAIT TILL HE DOES.
I'LL BE PATIENT.
DON'T WORRY, KIRITO.
I'VE GOT YOUR BACK.
Kirito: CONCENTRATE.
HOME IN ON HIS DRIVE TO KILL
LIKE LAST TIME.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I COULD FEEL
THEIR LUST FOR MURDER.
THAT'S HOW I NOTICED 'EM.
THE FIRST GUY WHO ATTACKED ME,
WHAT WAS HIS NAME?
Death Gun: KIRITO,
SOMEDAY I'LL KILL YOU PROPERLY.
Kirito: (GASPS)
Death Gun:
SOMEDAY I'LL KILL YOU PROPERLY.
Kirito: YAMIKAZE.
(YELLS)
Sinon: (GASPS)
Yamikaze: (GASPS)
(GASPS)
Sinon: KIRITO.
GOTCHA.
(GASPS)
IT'S UP TO YOU NOW, KIRITO.
Kirito: SHE DID IT.
NOW IT'S MY TURN. (GASPS)
(YELLS)
(GASPS)
Sinon: (GASPS) KIRITO.
Yui: DON'T WORRY, MOMMY.
NO MATTER HOW STRONG
HIS ENEMY IS, DADDY WONT LOSE.
HE'S DADDY, AFTER ALL.
Asuna: YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
Yui: TURN LEFT.
HIS ROOM IS EIGHT METERS DOWN.
Aki: KIRIGAYA?
Kirito: (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Asuna: KIRITO!
Aki: MISS YUUKI, RIGHT?
WE'VE BEEN EXPECTING YOU.
Asuna: IS SOMETHING WRONG
WITH KI‐‐I MEAN KAZUTO?
Aki: NO, HE'S OKAY.
I KNOW IT LOOKS BAD,
BUT HE'S NOT IN DANGER.
HIS HEART RATE SPIKED, IS ALL.
Asuna: HIS HEART RATE?
WHY? WHAT'S GOING ON?
Yui: MOMMY, LOOK TO YOUR RIGHT
AT THE MONITOR ON THE WALL.
I'M GOING TO PATCH IN
THE LIVE FOOTAGE
FROM THE MMO STREAM.
Aki: HUH?
Asuna: IS THAT KIRITO?
Aki: THAT'S KIRIGAYA'S AVATAR
FROM THE GAME
HE'S DIVING IN NOW?
Asuna: UH‐HUH. HE'S IN BATTLE.
I THINK THAT'S WHY
HIS HEART'S RACING SO MUCH.
(GASPS)
AN ESTOC.
(GASPS) THAT'S IT.
ONE OF LAUGHING COFFIN'S LEADERS
WAS A MASTER WITH AN ESTOC,
BUT WHAT WAS HE CALLED?
"STERBEN"?
ISN'T IT SUPPOSED TO BE STEVEN?
Aki: IT'S NOT.
Yui: SHE'S RIGHT.
Aki: IT'S A GERMAN WORD.
I KNOW IT.
IT'S A MEDICAL TERM WE USE.
IT'S PRONOUNCED "SHTERBEN."
Asuna: "SHTERBEN"?
Aki: IT MEANS "TO DIE."
IN HOSPITALS, WE USE THAT WORD
WHEN A PATIENT'S PASSED AWAY.
Asuna: (GASPS)
Kirito: (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Asuna: KIRITO.
Kirito: HEH.
THAT'S AN INTERESTING WEAPON
YOU'VE GOT THERE.
IF I'D KNOWN THERE WERE
METAL SWORDS IN "GGO,"
I WOULD HAVE GOTTEN
MY HANDS ON ONE.
Death Gun: YOU SHOULD
HAVE DONE YOUR HOMEWORK
BEFORE LOGGING IN,
BLACK SWORDSMAN.
I MADE THIS
WITH THE WEAPON CREATION SKILL.
IT CAN'T BE
ANY LONGER OR HEAVIER,
BUT IT DOES THE TRICK.
Kirito: WOW. IF THAT'S
THE BEST SWORD I CAN MAKE,
THEN I GUESS I COULDN'T MAKE ONE
I'D BE HAPPY WITH.
Death Gun: STILL INTO SWORDS
WITH HIGH STRENGTH REQUIREMENTS?
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED.
MUST BE PRETTY TOUGH FOR YOU,
HAVING TO TWIRL
THAT FLASHLIGHT AROUND.
(PHOTON SWORD HUMS)
Kirito: THIS THING'S
NOT AS BAD AS ALL THAT.
I ALWAYS WONDERED WHAT IT'D BE
LIKE TO FIGHT WITH ONE OF THESE.
BESIDES, A SWORD'S A SWORD.
IF I CAN SLASH YOU AND
BURN THROUGH YOUR H. P. WITH IT,
IT'S GOOD ENOUGH FOR ME.
Death Gun: (CHUCKLES)
YOU TALK A GOOD GAME,
BUT IT'S ALL TALK.
YOU SUCKED IN TOO MUCH
ROTTEN AIR FROM THE REAL WORLD.
THAT HALF‐ASS VORPAL STRIKE
YOU JUST PULLED,
IF THE OLD YOU SAW IT,
HE'D SHAKE HIS HEAD.
Kirito: MAYBE SO,
BUT THE SAME GOES FOR YOU, TOO.
YOU'RE LIVING IN THE PAST.
I BET YOU THINK YOU'RE STILL
A MEMBER OF LAUGHING COFFIN.
Death Gun: YOU REMEMBER.
I'M IMPRESSED.
THEN I GUESS YOU UNDERSTAND
THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
I'M A GENUINE RED PLAYER,
WHILE YOU ARE NOT.
YOU KILLED
ONLY BECAUSE YOU WERE SCARED,
SCARED AND DESPERATE TO SURVIVE.
AND INSTEAD OF FACING IT,
I BET YOU TRIED
TO FORGET IT EVEN HAPPENED,
JUST LIKE A COWARD.
Kirito: (GASPS)
I MIGHT BE A COWARD,
BUT STILL, I'LL STOP YOU
FROM KILLING AGAIN.
I FIGURED OUT HOW ZXE‐D
AND THE OTHERS WERE MURDERED.
IT'S GOT NOTHING TO DO
WITH THAT HANDGUN OF YOURS,
AND YOU DON'T HAVE
SPECIAL POWERS EITHER.
Death Gun:
HOW'D THOSE PEOPLE DIE THEN?
Kirito: BACK AT THE TERMINALS
AT THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE,
YOU USED THAT CLOAK
TO SCOPE OUT THE ADDRESSES
OF THE B. o. B. CONTESTANTS.
THEN YOU HAD SOMEONE
BREAK INTO THEIR APARTMENTS
AND TIMED IT SO WHEN YOU FIRED,
THEY'D INJECT A DRUG INTO 'EM,
MAKING IT LOOK
LIKE THEY DIED OF HEART FAILURE.
THAT'S HOW YOU DID IT.
THE MINISTRY
OF INTERNAL AFFAIRS
HAS THE IN‐GAME
AND REAL‐WORLD INFO
OF EVERY SINGLE PLAYER
FROM "S. A. O."
ONCE THEY GET YOUR HANDLE,
THEY'LL FIND OUT YOUR REAL NAME,
YOUR REAL ADDRESS, AND ALL
THE EVIL SHIT YOU'VE EVER DONE.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME.
IT'S ALL OVER FOR YOU,
SO LOG OUT,
AND TURN YOURSELF IN.
Death Gun: YOU THINK YOU'VE
GOT IT ALL FIGURED OUT,
BUT YOU DON'T.
AND YOU CAN'T STOP ME.
WANT TO KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE I KNOW YOU'LL NEVER
REMEMBER WHAT MY HANDLE WAS.
Kirito: YOU THINK SO?
WHAT MAKES YOU SO SURE I WON'T?
Death Gun: (CHUCKLES)
YOU DON'T EVEN REMEMBER
THE REASON YOU FORGOT IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THINK BACK.
AFTER THAT BATTLE
BETWEEN YOUR GROUP AND MINE,
I TRIED TO TELL YOU MY NAME,
BUT YOU SAID...
Kirito: THERE'S NO POINT
IN GIVING ME YOUR NAME.
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW IT.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
I'LL NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN.
(GASPS)
Death Gun: YOU CAN'T
REMEMBER MY HANDLE,
AND YOU NEVER WILL.
I NEVER GAVE IT TO YOU,
AND NOW I'M GOING
TO CUT YOU DOWN.
I'LL LEAVE YOU LYING HERE,
WATCHING HELPLESSLY
AS I KILL THE GIRL,
AND YOU CAN'T STOP ME!
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
STINGS, DOESN'T IT?
THIS IS MADE FROM THE BEST METAL
YOU CAN GET IN THE GAME.
IT'S ARMOR PLATING
FROM A SPACE BATTLESHIP.
(LAUGHS)