Host: ONLY THREE DAYS LEFT
TILL THE NEW YEAR,
AND I HOPE YOU'RE ALL
ENJOYING YOUR HOLIDAY.
Leafa: HEY,
WERE YOU UP LATE AGAIN?
Kirito: YEAH,
FOR A MECHATRONICS PROJECT
FOR SCHOOL.
Leafa: MECHA‐WHAT? SOUNDS FUN.
Host: ...FROM THE TRAFFIC
INFORMATION CENTER.
‐ Leafa: KAZUTO.
‐ Kirito: HMM?
Leafa: YOU SEE THIS YET?
‐ (CUP CLATTERS)
‐ Kirito: WHAT THE?!
THE HOLY SWORD EXCALIBUR
HAS BEEN FOUND IN "A. L. O."?!
AW, MAN, THAT SUCKS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
SOMEONE ELSE BEAT US TO IT.
Leafa: READ THE ARTICLE, DOOFUS.
IT SAYS IT'S BEEN FOUND, IS ALL.
NO ONE'S ACTUALLY GOT IT YET.
Kirito: OH.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
DON'T SCARE ME LIKE THAT.
Leafa: (CHUCKLES)
Kirito: A COUPLE MONTHS AGO
ON THE ARUN PLAINS,
LEAFA, YUI, AND ME GOT SWALLOWED
BY A BIG‐ASS MONSTER WORM.
IT DROPPED US IN AN UNDERGROUND
REALM CALLED JOTUNHEIM.
WE LOOKED AROUND FOR A BIT
AND CAME ACROSS THIS FOUR‐ARMED
HUMANOID MONSTER.
IT WAS FIGHTING ANOTHER MONSTER
THAT LOOKED LIKE A CROSS
BETWEEN AN ELEPHANT
AND A JELLYFISH.
GO FIGURE. LEAFA FELT SORRY
FOR THE JELLY‐PHANT THING
AND TOLD ME TO GO SAVE IT.
I LURED FOUR ARMS
ONTO THIS FROZEN LAKE,
AND IT FELL THROUGH THE ICE.
THEN THE JELLY‐PHANT
TOOK CARE OF IT.
LEAFA DECIDED TO CALL IT TONKY,
AND SUDDENLY IT TRANSFORMED
INTO AN EVEN‐WEIRDER‐LOOKING
THING WITH EIGHT WINGS.
WE HOPPED ON ITS BACK,
AND IT TOOK US TO A PASSAGEWAY
LEADING TO THE SURFACE WORLD.
ON THE WAY UP WAS WHEN WE
SAW IT, AN UPSIDE‐DOWN PYRAMID
HANGING FROM THE ROOTS
OF THE WORLD TREE
AND A LONG, GOLDEN SWORD
SHIMMERING INSIDE.
EXCALIBUR.
I WAS PLANNING ON GOING BACK
FOR IT SOMEDAY, BUT NOW...
Leafa: IT'D BE A NICE BREAK
FROM ALL THAT FLOOR‐CLEARING
YOU'RE DOING IN NEW AINCRAD.
Kirito: THIS ARTICLE
DOESN'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT HOW THEY FOUND IT.
PLAYERS CAN'T FLY
IN JOTUNHEIM, REMEMBER?
BUT THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO SPOT EXCALIBUR.
THAT THING'S TOO HIGH UP TO SEE.
Leafa: UNLESS THEY RESCUED
ONE OF TONKY'S FRIENDS,
HITCHED A RIDE,
AND TRIGGERED THE QUEST FLAG.
IF WE COULD DO IT,
SO COULD SOMEONE ELSE.
Kirito: I GUESS
THAT MAKES SENSE,
ALTHOUGH WHO'D TRUST A CREEPY‐‐
‐ Leafa: (GROWLS)
‐ Kirito: (GRUNTS)
UH, I MEAN WHO'D TRUST
SUCH A UNIQUE MONSTER
‐ UNLESS THEY HAD WEIRD TA‐‐
‐ Leafa: (GROWLS)
Kirito: I MEAN
A WEIRDLY BIG HEART.
(BUBBLES BUBBLING)
SOMEONE JUST LIKE YOU, SIS.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
Leafa: HE IS NOT CREEPY.
HE'S ADORABLE.
ANYWAY, THE WHOLE POINT
OF SHOWING YOU THAT
WAS TO GET YOU GOING.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SOMEONE
GRINDS THROUGH THAT DUNGEON
AND GETS THE SWORD.
Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT.
CLOCK'S TICKING.
Leafa: SO WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
Kirito: (CLEARS THROAT)
SUGU, GETTING RARE ITEMS
ISN'T THE POINT OF IT.
IF THAT'S ALL YOU PLAY FOR,
YOU'RE MISSING OUT.
Leafa: YEAH,
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE'S FUNNER THINGS TO DO
THAN BOOSTING STATS.
Kirito: I WASN'T FINISHED.
I THINK TONKY
WANTED US TO FIND IT,
AND THAT'S WHY
HE SHOWED US WHERE IT WAS.
FOR SOME REASON, HE NEEDS US
TO CLEAR THAT DUNGEON,
SO IT'S UP TO US
TO MAKE HIS WISH COME TRUE.
TONKY'S OUR FRIEND,
AND THERE'S NO WAY
I'M TURNING MY BACK ON A FRIEND.
Leafa: MMM!
A MINUTE AGO,
YOU CALLED YOUR FRIEND CREEPY.
Kirito: MM.
I MEANT CREEPY COOL.
ANYWAY, YOU IN?
Leafa: SURE. I DON'T HAVE
PRACTICE 'CAUSE OF THE HOLIDAYS.
Kirito: AWESOME.
OKAY, WE'LL NEED SEVEN OTHERS.
WE DON'T WANT TO OVERLOAD TONKY.
FOR STARTERS, WE GOT
YOU, ME, AND ASUNA.
THEN THERE'S KLEIN,
LIZ, AND SILICA.
WE NEED ONE MORE PERSON.
AGIL'S GOTTA WORK TONIGHT.
CHRYSHEIGHT'S
NOT LEVELED UP YET.
RECON'S GRINDING
IN SYLPH TERRITORY.
Leafa: OH, I KNOW.
LET'S ASK SINON TO COME ALONG.
Kirito: GREAT IDEA, SIS.
Leafa: WHAT'D YOU EXPECT?
I'LL MESSAGE 'EM RIGHT NOW,
EXCEPT FOR ASUNA.
I'LL LEAVE THAT TO YOU.
Kirito: OKAY.
Asuna: (SIGHS)
I WISH I COULD SEE KIRITO AGAIN
BEFORE I GO VISIT
MY GRANDPARENTS.
(RINGTONE CHIMING)
H‐HI, KIRITO.
Kirito: MORNING, ASUNA.
SORRY TO CALL SO EARLY.
WE WERE PLANNING
ON GOING ON A QUEST
IN "A. L. O." THIS AFTERNOON.
YOU WANT TO GO?
Asuna: YEAH, I'LL TOTALLY GO.
I'M FREE ALL DAY TODAY.
Kirito: COOL. I'LL TEXT YOU
THE TIME AND PLACE,
SO KEEP AN EYE OUT FOR IT.
Asuna: YOU KNOW I WILL.
SEE YOU IN A LITTLE WHILE, THEN.
YES.
Klein: (SIGHS)
‐ (LAUGHS)
‐ Silica: HEY, KLEIN,
DO YOU GET TO TAKE VACATION
FOR NEW YEAR'S?
Klein: BEEN ON IT
SINCE YESTERDAY.
EVEN IF I WANTED TO WORK‐‐
AND I DON'T‐‐
THERE'S NO SHIPMENTS
THIS TIME OF YEAR.
YOU KNOW WHAT
MY CHEAP‐ASS BOSS SAID?
"BE THANKFUL YOU GOT
A JOB WHERE YOU GET
A WHOLE WEEK OFF
FOR NEW YEAR'S,"
BRAGGING ABOUT IT LIKE HE
WAS DOING US A FAVOR.
AND SPEAKING OF FAVORS,
IF WE DO MANAGE
TO SNAG EXCALIBUR TODAY,
HOW ABOUT DOING ME A SOLID
AND HELPING ME GET MY HANDS
ON THE SOUL BLADE KAGUZUCHI?
Kirito: SERIOUSLY?
THAT DUNGEON'S LIKE
A FRIGGING OVEN, MAN.
Klein: YEAH, WELL,
I'M GOING TO JOTUNHEIM FOR YOU,
WHERE IT'S COLDER
THAN THE ASS‐END OF AN ICE POP.
Sinon: YOU KNOW, I WANT
SOMETHING OUT OF THIS, TOO,
THE SHEKHINAH BOW.
Kirito: UH, YOUR AVATAR'S
TWO WEEKS OLD,
AND ALREADY YOU'RE GUNNING
FOR A LEGENDARY WEAPON?
Sinon: YEAH, WELL, THAT BOW
LIZ MADE ME IS GREAT AND ALL,
BUT I NEED SOMETHING
WITH A LITTLE MORE RANGE.
Lisbeth: OH, YEAH?
THEN WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU
USING A BOW IN "A. L. O." FOR?
THEIR RANGE FALLS
BETWEEN SPEARS AND MAGIC.
YOU'RE LIKE THE ONLY PLAYER
WHO WANTS TO USE THESE THINGS
TO SNIPE FROM 100 METERS.
Sinon: IF I HAD MY WAY,
I'D WANT DOUBLE
THAT RANGE AT LEAST.
Lisbeth: (GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Leafa: WE'RE BACK, GUYS.
Asuna: THANKS FOR WAITING.
Silica: WE THOUGHT
YOU WERE NEVER COMING BACK.
Klein: WHAT'S UP?
YOU GET LOST OR SOMETHING?
Yui: NOT AT ALL.
WE WERE GATHERING INFORMATION
WHILE WE SHOPPED.
WE TALKED TO A WHOLE BUNCH
OF PEOPLE, DADDY,
AND SO FAR,
NOT ONE PLAYER OR PARTY
HAS REACHED THAT DUNGEON YET.
Kirito: REALLY?
WELL, THEN HOW THE HECK DO THEY
KNOW WHERE EXCALIBUR'S AT?
Yui: THAT'S THE THING, DADDY.
NO ONE REALLY KNOWS WHERE IT IS.
APPARENTLY THEY FOUND
A DIFFERENT QUEST
THAN THE ONE TONKY SHOWED US.
THEY MET AN NPC WHO TOLD THEM IF
THEY FINISHED THIS OTHER QUEST,
THEY'D GET EXCALIBUR
AS THE REWARD.
Asuna: AND FROM WHAT WE HEARD,
THE QUEST THEY'RE GOING ON
ISN'T VERY PLEASANT.
INSTEAD OF A DELIVERY QUEST
OR AN ESCORT QUEST,
IT'S A KILL QUEST,
JUST SLAUGHTERING MONSTERS.
EVERYONE IN JOTUNHEIM
IS OUT THERE RIGHT NOW
KILLING AS MANY AS THEY CAN.
Kirito: YEAH, THAT DOESN'T EVEN
SOUND CLOSE TO BEING PLEASANT.
Klein: THIS WHOLE THING
SOUNDS SKETCHY TO ME, GUYS.
HERE'S WHAT WE KNOW.
THERE'S A DUNGEON IN THE SKY
WITH EXCALIBUR LOCKED UP
AT THE BOTTOM OF IT.
TO GET TO IT,
YOU GOTTA FIGHT YOUR WAY
THROUGH A BUNCH OF MONSTERS.
BUT NOW WE GOT AN NPC
OFFERING IT UP
AS A KILL‐QUEST REWARD?
THAT'S BIZARRE.
Silica: NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
‐ THAT IS WEIRD.
‐ Pina: (COOS)
Silica: THE NPC's NOT
SHOWING ANYONE TO THE DUNGEON,
BUT THAT'S WHERE THE SWORD IS.
All: ( SIGH )
Sinon: WELL, I'M SURE
WE'LL FIND OUT WHY
ONCE WE GET THERE.
Lisbeth: ALL RIGHTY.
YOUR WEAPONS ARE ALL RESTORED
AND READY FOR ACTION.
Klein: EVEN THOUGH
OUR PARTY'S FULL OF HOTNESS,
WE'RE STILL A BUNCH
OF GEAR‐TOTING MEATHEADS.
Lisbeth: IF YOU
WANNA SWITCH IT UP,
YOU COULD ALWAYS
BOOST YOUR MAGIC.
Klein: HA! KEEP DREAMING.
A REAL SAMURAI, HE WOULDN'T
BE CAUGHT DEAD USING MAGIC.
CODE OF HONOR.
Lisbeth: CODE OF HONOR, HUH?
KNOW WHAT SAMURAI'S ARE
CLASSIFIED AS IN RPGs?
THEY'RE BOTH WARRIORS
AND BLACK‐MAGIC USERS.
Klein: PLEASE.
I'D RATHER BUST MY SWORD
AND QUIT BEING A SAMURAI
THAN USE MAGIC, DOLL.
Silica: I DON'T KNOW, KLEIN.
IF I REMEMBER RIGHT,
DIDN'T YOU USE A FLAME‐SWORD
SKILL THE OTHER DAY?
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU ACTIVATE IT,
YOU ARE USING PART MAGIC.
Klein: NO WAY. REALLY?
Yui: YES, KLEIN.
WHAT SILICA SAID IS TRUE.
REMEMBER THE MAY UPDATE?
IT BROUGHT A WHOLE BUNCH
OF NEW SWORD SKILLS TO "A. L. O."
SOME ARE PHYSICAL,
AND OTHERS ARE ADVANCED,
LIKE EARTH, WATER, FIRE,
WIND, DARK, AND DIVINE,
ALL OF WHICH
ARE MAGICAL ATTRIBUTES.
Klein: FIRE'S MAGICAL, TOO, HUH?
Lisbeth: OKAY, EX‐SAMURAI,
YOU NEED HELP
BUSTING THAT SWORD?
Klein: (GASPS)
DUDE, BACK ME UP HERE.
Kirito: WELL, SINCE YOU DON'T
CHANT WHEN USING SWORD SKILLS,
I GUESS IT'S NOT THE SAME.
Lisbeth: I'LL LET IT
SLIDE THIS TIME. HEH.
Klein: (SIGHS)
Yui: (GIGGLES)
Kirito: I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOU GUYS HELPING ME OUT
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
SERIOUSLY, YOU DON'T KNOW
HOW MUCH THIS MEANS TO ME.
ALL RIGHT, ARE YOU READY?
All: YEAH!
(FOOTSTEPS CLACKING)
Lisbeth: GOD.
HOW MANY STEPS DOES
THIS THING HAVE, ANYWAY?
Leafa: I KNOW. I BET THE TOWER
ON THE DUNGEON FLOOR
OF NEW AINCRAD DOESN'T
EVEN HAVE AS MANY AS THIS.
Kirito: OH, COME ON.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
IF WE TOOK THE NORMAL ROUTE
TO JOTUNHEIM,
IT'D TAKE AT LEAST TWO HOURS.
THIS WAY,
IT'S JUST FIVE MINUTES.
INSTEAD OF COMPLAINING
ABOUT THE STEPS,
YOU SHOULD BE THANKING ME
FOR SHOWING YOU GUYS
THIS RAD SHORTCUT.
Sinon: YEAH, YEAH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S STILL A PAIN IN THE BUTT.
Kirito: I GOT YOUR PAIN
IN THE BUTT.
Sinon: (GASPS, SHRIEKS)
WHY, YOU...
Kirito: (CHUCKLES)
Sinon: DUMB‐ASS.
DO THAT AGAIN,
AND YOU GET A FIRE ARROW
IN YOUR PIEHOLE.
Pina: (COOS)
Klein: BROTHER,
YOU GOT BALLS OF STEEL, NO JOKE.
FREEZING.
Silica: WOWSERS.
Pina: (COOS)
Sinon: AMAZING.
Klein: (SHIVERING)
AREN'T YOU COLD?
Asuna: OATH, SHARLE, RAISE,
VIND, BARD, HARL‐CA, STOLES.
BETTER?
I CAST A FREEZE‐RESISTANCE SPELL
OVER US.
Leafa: (WHISTLES)
(DISTANT TRUMPETING)
Tonky: (TRUMPETING)
Yui: TONKY, UP HERE!
Klein: JESUS. (SHIVERS)
Kirito: TAKE IT EASY, KLEIN.
HE DOESN'T LOOK IT,
BUT HE'S A VEGETARIAN.
Leafa: WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
WHEN I BROUGHT HIM SOME FISH
FROM ABOVEGROUND,
HE SCARFED IT ALL DOWN
IN ONE BITE.
Klein: UH‐OH.
WHAT'S HE DOING?
Kirito: HE'S TELLING YOU
TO GET ON HIS BACK IS ALL.
Klein: DUDE, NO WAY.
NO WAY IN HELL.
MY GRANDPA'S DYING WORDS
WERE DON'T RIDE IN FOREIGN CARS
OR ON FLYING CTHULHU ELEPHANTS.
Kirito: IS HE
THE SAME DEAD GRANDPA
WHOSE DRIED FIGS WE WERE EATING
AT DICEY'S THE OTHER DAY?
STOP FARTING AROUND,
AND GET ON.
Klein: IF IT EATS ME, MAN...
Lisbeth: THIS IS GONNA BE FUN.
Klein: WE'RE SO DEAD.
Kirito: THANKS A LOT
FOR DOING THIS, TONKY.
Leafa: ALL RIGHT, TONKY.
EVERYONE'S ONBOARD,
SO TAKE US TO THAT DUNGEON!
Tonky: (TRUMPETS)
Lisbeth: WOW.
I WONDER WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
IF YOU FELL FROM WAY UP HERE?
Asuna: THE SAME THING
THAT HAPPENED
WHEN A CERTAIN SOMEONE
DECIDED TO GET
TO THE NEXT LEVEL OF AINCRAD
BY CLIMBING THE OUTER PILLARS.
SO HOW 'BOUT IT, WONDER KLUTZ?
CARE TO SHOW THE LADY?
Kirito: NAH. I THINK I'LL PASS.
BUT MAYBE ONE OF OUR
MORE CATLIKE FRIENDS
WOULD LIKE TO TAKE A SHOT.
Both: NOPE, NOPE,
NOPE, NOPE, NOPE.
‐ Tonky: (BELLOWS)
‐ All: EH?
(SCREAMING)
Leafa: (LAUGHS)
YAH‐HAH! (LAUGHS)
All: (GROANING)
Leafa: KAZUTO, GET UP HERE.
CHECK IT OUT.
Players: (YELLING)
Jelly‐phant: (WAILING)
Humanoid: (ROARS)
Asuna: MY GOD.
I‐‐I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THEY FIGURED OUT HOW TO MAKE
THAT MONSTER FIGHT FOR THEM.
Silica: NO, THERE'S GOTTA
BE ANOTHER REASON.
IT'S NOT POSSIBLE
TO TAME MONSTERS IN THIS GAME,
NOT EVEN IF YOU'RE
A CAIT SITH MASTER TAMER
WITH A FULL POWER BOOST
AND SPECIAL EQUIPMENT.
Pina: (SQUAWKS)
Klein: THEN THEY'RE
LEECHING OFF THE MONSTER?
NO, WAIT. THEY'RE NOT LEECHING.
PIGGYBACKING, YEAH, THAT'S IT.
SEE, THAT GROUP'S
GOT OL' FOUR‐ARMS THERE
DOING ALL THE HEAVY LIFTING
AND SNIPING AT THE JELLY‐PHANT
WHEN THEY GET AN OPENING.
Sinon: BUT IS IT THAT EASY
TO CONTROL A MONSTER'S AGGRO?
IT'S IGNORING EVERYONE ELSE.
Jelly‐phant: (WAILS)
Tonky: (BELLOWS)
Humanoid: (GROANS)
Kirito: HOW COME THEY'RE NOT
TAKING ON THAT FOUR‐ARMED DUDE?
WHERE'S EVERYONE GOING?
Asuna: HEY, YOU GUYS, LOOK.
Klein: WHAT THE HELL'S
GOING ON DOWN THERE?
Lisbeth: AFTER WHAT WE JUST SAW
AND HOW IT WENT DOWN,
IT SHOULD BE
PRETTY OBVIOUS WHAT IT IS.
I HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT WE'RE LOOKING
AT THAT KILL QUEST
ASUNA TOLD US ABOUT.
EVEN THOUGH IT'S A QUEST,
HELPING THESE FOUR‐ARMED FREAKS
MURDER TONKY'S FRIENDS
IS DISGUSTING.
‐ (GASPS)
‐ HMM?
Klein: DAMN, SHE'S TALL.
All: (GASP)
Urd: GREETINGS.
I AM URD, QUEEN OF THE LAKE.
YOU HAVE BONDED WITH MY KINSMAN,
AND I AM GRATEFUL.
MY TWO YOUNGER SISTERS AND I
HAVE SPOKEN AT LENGTH,
AND WE HAVE A REQUEST FOR YOU.
IF YOU WOULD BE SO KIND,
WE ASK THAT YOU SAVE OUR LANDS
FROM THE FROST GIANTS.
Yui: DADDY, SHE'S AN NPC.
THERE'S SOMETHING STRANGE
ABOUT HER, THOUGH.
HER SPEECH PATTERN
DOESN'T FOLLOW
THE SAME SET RESPONSE ROUTINES
THAT A NORMAL NPC's WOULD.
HER CORE PROGRAMMING
IS CONNECTED
TO THE LANGUAGE ENGINE MODULE
OF THE GAME.
Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
IS SHE SOME KIND OF A. I.?
Yui: YES, DADDY, SHE IS.
Urd: IN THE PAST,
JOTUNHEIM WAS SIMILAR
TO YOUR ALFHEIM,
COVERED IN LUSH GREENERY
AND BEAUTIFUL LAKES.
IT BASKED IN THE BLESSINGS
OF YGGDRASIL, THE WORLD TREE.
WE, THE HILL GIANTS,
LIVED IN PEACE AND HARMONY
WITH OUR KINFOLK, THE CREATURES.
FAR BELOW
THE SPLENDOR OF JOTUNHEIM
IS A REALM OF ICE AND SNOW
KNOWN AS NIFLHEIM.
THRYMR,
KING OF THE FROST GIANTS,
RULES THAT LAND.
HE SHATTERED OUR PEACE
BY CASTING EXCALIBUR,
THE SWORD THAT SLICES
THROUGH WOOD AND IRON,
INTO THE WELL OF URD,
THE HEART OF OUR LAND.
IT SEVERED THE THICKEST ROOTS
OF THE WORLD TREE.
IN AN INSTANT,
JOTUNHEIM LOST THE BLESSINGS
IT RECEIVED FROM YGGDRASIL.
Kirito: I WAS RIGHT, EXCALIBUR.
Urd: UNDER THRYMR'S COMMAND,
THE FROST GIANTS
MARCHED ON JOTUNHEIM
AND OVERWHELMED OUR DEFENSES.
THEIR FORTRESSES AND CASTLES
SOON BLIGHTED OUR LAND,
AND SCORES OF MY PEOPLE
WERE CAPTURED AND IMPRISONED.
ONCE THEY SEIZED CONTROL,
THEY BUILT THRYMHEIM,
THEIR LARGEST CASTLE,
ATOP THE MASS OF ICE
ONCE KNOWN AS THE WELL OF URD.
DURING THE CHAOS,
MY SISTERS AND I
ESCAPED TO THE BOTTOM
OF A FROZEN LAKE.
HOWEVER, WE NO LONGER
HAVE THE POWER WE ONCE HAD.
THE FROST GIANTS ARE NOT
SATISFIED WITH THEIR SPOILS.
THEY WISH TO ANNIHILATE OUR KIN,
THE CREATURES
THAT POPULATE OUR REALM.
IF THEY SUCCEED, MY POWERS
WILL BE EXTINGUISHED,
AND THRYMHEIM WILL RISE
TO THE NEXT WORLD,
YOUR WORLD, ALFHEIM.
Klein: (GASPS) HOLD THE PHONE.
YOU'RE TELLING US
THAT ONCE THEY'RE DONE HERE,
THEY'RE GONNA GO UP
AND DESTROY ARUN?
Urd: YES, THAT IS
THEIR INTENTION.
KING THRYMR WILL SEAL ALFHEIM
IN ICE AND CONTINUE ON
UNTIL HE REACHES
THE TOP OF YGGDRASIL.
ONCE HE REACHES IT,
HE WILL TAKE
THE GOLDEN APPLE GROWING THERE.
THRYMR AND HIS GENERALS
HAVE GROWN FRUSTRATED
BY THE TIME IT IS TAKING
TO WIPE OUT MY KINFOLK,
SO THEY HAVE TURNED
TO YOUR PEOPLE, THE FAERIES,
FOR ASSISTANCE
IN THEIR MURDEROUS PLOT.
YOUR KIND HUNTS
OUR KINFOLK TO EXTINCTION,
LURED BY THE OFFER
OF EXCALIBUR AS A REWARD.
HOWEVER, KING THRYMR
CANNOT BESTOW
THAT SWORD UNTO OTHERS,
FOR IF EXCALIBUR
EVER LEAVES THRYMHEIM,
THE BLESSINGS OF YGGDRASIL
WILL RETURN TO THIS LAND,
AND THEIR CASTLE WILL VANISH
AS A MIST UPON A MEADOW.
Lisbeth: BUT‐‐BUT THEN...
WHAT KIND OF QUEST IS IT WHEN
THE REWARD FOR IT'S A TOTAL LIE?
HOW IS HE GONNA
GET AWAY WITH IT?
Urd: MOST LIKELY,
HE WILL AWARD THE VICTOR
A SWORD CALLED CALIBURN,
WHOSE APPEARANCE
IS IDENTICAL TO EXCALIBUR.
Leafa: BUT THAT'S CHEATING.
IF HE'S A KING, DOESN'T HE
HAVE A CODE OF HONOR?
Urd: UNFORTUNATELY,
CHEATING AND FALSEHOODS
ARE THRYMR'S
MOST POWERFUL ASSETS.
HOWEVER, HE HAS MADE
ONE GREAT MISTAKE.
IN HIS EAGERNESS
TO SLAUGHTER MY KIN,
HE HAS SENT A NUMBER OF
HIS GIANTS DOWN FROM THRYMHEIM
TO MARSHAL YOUR KIND FOR BATTLE.
AT THIS MOMENT,
THE DEFENSES OF HIS CASTLE
ARE WEAKER
THAN THEY HAVE EVER BEEN.
Kirito: THERE'S OUR SHOT.
Urd: ONCE THE STONE
IN THE AMULET TURNS BLACK,
IT WILL MEAN ALL MY KINFOLK
HAVE BEEN SLAIN
AND MY POWERS HAVE LEFT ME.
GOOD FAERIES,
INFILTRATE THRYMHEIM,
REMOVE EXCALIBUR
FROM ITS PLINTH,
AND SAVE MY REALM.
I AM COUNTING ON YOU,
GOOD FAERIES.
Tonky: (BELLOWS)
Asuna: THIS IS TURNING INTO
A BIGGER DEAL THAN WE THOUGHT.
Sinon: IS THIS STILL
CONSIDERED A QUEST?
'CAUSE IT'S KINDA TURNED INTO
SOMETHING WAY MORE EPIC
THAN A PLAIN OLD QUEST.
YOU HEARD HER. SHE SAID
IF THE CREATURES IN THIS WORLD
GET KILLED OFF,
THE FROST GIANTS'LL TAKE OVER
THE SURFACE NEXT.
Kirito: YEAH, I KNOW,
BUT I DOUBT THE ADMINS
WOULD LET THAT HAPPEN
WITHOUT SOME KIND OF UPDATE
OR WARNING OR SOMETHING.
I MEAN, NORMALLY,
THEY'D LET PLAYERS KNOW
A WEEK AHEAD OF TIME.
Leafa: WHATEVER. WE'RE GONNA
FINISH THIS QUEST FOR TONKY.
RIGHT, KAZUTO?
Kirito: YOU KNOW IT.
WE WERE GONNA STORM THE CASTLE
AND GRAB EXCALIBUR ANYWAY.
IT'LL BE EASY IF
THE CASTLE'S DEFENSES ARE DOWN.
HELPING TONKY AND HIS FRIENDS
OUT, THAT'S A BONUS.
Kirito: HERE WE GO, GUYS!
OUR LAST BIG QUEST OF THE YEAR!
LET'S SPANK THIS THING
AND SCORE US A SPOT
ON THE FRONT PAGE
OF MMO TOMORROW!
All: YEAH!
Tonky: (BELLOWS)
Leafa: DON'T YOU WORRY, TONKY.
WE'LL GET
YOUR HOME BACK FOR YOU.
IT'LL BE GOOD AS NEW. PROMISE.
Kirito: HERE WE GO.