Josuke: You think you’ve got me cornered,
but i’ve already implemented my tactics.
Keicho: Eh?
What the--
( glass tinkling )
( Okuyasu gasps )
♪
( Flames crackling )
( Josuke sighs ) I really hate to say it,
but okuyasu’s brother just about took me out for good.
Koichi, I think it’s high time we got the hell out of here.
Koichi: Huh? But what about the bow and arrow he had?
Where did it go?
Josuke: Good memory.
Bastard must have hid it somewhere
after he dragged you up the stairs.
- Don’t tell me you wanna-- - koichi: Yeah.
Josuke: Hold off on looking for it.
If their dad bought this place, he may still be around.
Plus, i’m too badly hurt to be of much help to you.
Let’s just leave it be for now.
koichi: No! We can’t just do nothing.
Look, the only reason i’m alive right now
is because you healed my wounds with your stand,
but think about it.
If somebody else gets shot with that bow and arrow,
let’s face it. They’re probably gonna die.
- Is that what you want? - ( Josuke grunts )
Koichi: You can stay here and rest up.
Don’t worry about me.
I’ll find it by myself.
And, truth be told, i’m not so sure
their dad even lives in this house anymore.
I mean, if he was living here,
he would have come out by now, right?
( Sighs )
( Stairs creaking )
Josuke: He may not look it,
but koichi has a hell of a lot of guts,
at least when things get tough or he’s not in his head.
But that won’t mean a thing if we don’t make it out of here.
We need to leave as fast as we can.
- ( Koichi shudders ) - Josuke: Hey!
Koichi: Oh! It’s you.
What? You trying to stop me?!
Josuke: Not a chance.
we’re gonna snap that bow and arrow in two,
then say goodbye to this hellhole together.
( Koichi sighs )
♪
( Rattling )
( Grunting )
♪
( Koichi sighs )
( Stairs creak )
There’s an attic.
The bow and arrow’s probably up here.
♪
( Gasps )
There it is, the bow and arrow,
and it’s just hanging on the wall.
- ( Scraping ) - ( Gasps )
( Creature groaning )
Josuke: That doesn’t sound good.
Something must be in there.
( Koichi gasps )
- ( Chain rattles ) - ( Gasps )
josuke: Well, at least it’s chained up, whatever it is.
Koichi: You think it could be a dog?
’cause it’s definitely not a person.
( Creature groaning )
Koichi: Well, if it is, it sure isn’t happy.
( Scraping )
( Both sigh )
( Door creaking )
( Koichi shudders )
( Creature wails )
Koichi: What are we supposed to do?
- I’m too scared to think. - Josuke: Why are you asking me?
I voted to leave this house of horrors.
Koichi: I know, but...
Josuke: We can’t just turn back now.
All right, koichi, on the count of three,
I want you to bust the door open with everything you’ve got.
That should scare it.
Then i’ll run over as fast as I can
and break that bow and arrow in half. You got it?
( Koichi sighs ) Yeah.
( Creature growling )
Josuke: Let’s go.
One, two...
Three!
( Creature roars )
- ( Koichi screams ) - ( Josuke gasps )
What the hell?!
- ( Koichi screaming ) - Josuke: Koichi!
- Koichi: Help me! - Josuke: Wait a minute.
That thing is no stand.
It’s a real hand attached to a real funky-looking arm!
Koichi: Help me, please!
Shining diamond: Dora!
( Josuke gasps )
Koichi: Yuck.
Josuke: I wasn’t trying to sever it.
( Creature grunting )
( Sobbing )
( Koichi gasps )
( Heart beating )
( Both gasp )
( Koichi gags )
( Creature grunting )
( Growls )
( Koichi shudders )
( Both wail )
( Creature chewing )
josuke: Hey, koichi, what the hell is that thing?
I can’t believe something like that
was living right under our noses.
( Koichi groans ) Gross.
Keicho: So you found him.
That was never supposed to happen.
( Panting )
Josuke: You again?
( Keicho sighs )
It’s a long story,
but he’s our father, if you can believe it.
and right now, he needs these more than you.
Koichi: Why’s he grabbing the bow and arrow?
Keicho: It’s imperative that I find more stand users
for my father, so no one is getting these.
Come at me with all your might if you must.
I’ll protect ’em until the bitter end.
Josuke: So did a disease do this to your dad?
Keicho: A disease? You’re joking.
Dad is in excellent health, minus the warts.
He even has a hearty appetite.
But all he does is moan.
it’s safe to say he has no idea i’m his son.
Josuke: So you’ve been searching for a stand user
with the power to cure your father.
Keicho: To cure him?
( Laughs )
What, are you offering?
’cause you’re not needed.
( Laughing )
( Crying )
You’re wrong.
I’ve been searching for a stand user
who can kill my father, but at this point,
I doubt it’ll ever happen.
No matter what I do, dad won’t die.
I could bash his head in
or chop his body into a million tiny pieces.
Even slicing him to ribbons won’t kill him.
( Mr. Nijimura groaning )
( Nails scratching )
Keicho: I just want to end his suffering.
As a kid, I swore to do everything in my power
to make that happen, but I need the bow and arrow
in order to make good on my promise to him.
If I hand these over to you,
dad will be a freak for all eternity...
Suffering, all because some bastard named dio
decided to implant cells in his skull
and make my dad a monster!
Josuke: Hold on! Did you say, "dio"?
The guy from Mr. Jotaro’s story.
( Mr. Nijimura grunts )
Keicho: Indulge me by listening to how things used to be,
josuke higashkita.
Although what i’m about to tell you
is related to your life as well.
( Koichi gasps )
Keicho: Everything began 11 years ago.
1988 was the beginning of the end.
I was seven that year,
and my brother okuyasu was just four.
We were living in Tokyo during this time.
It was the middle of the bubble economy,
and spirits were high.
Well, the spirits of everyone except my father.
Mom fell sick and died,
and dad’s business went under.
he was buried under a mountain of debt.
( Slap echoes )
He’d often beat us for no reason.
He was the walking definition of a loser.
That’s when everything changed.
Out of the blue,
a seemingly endless supply of cash starting rolling in.
And on top of that,
there were jewels and precious metals,
but dad didn’t have a job to speak of.
After some research,
I found out the truth.
My father had made a dark deal.
he sold his own soul to a man by the name of dio.
He became dio’s lackey for monetary gain.
( Koichi gasps )
Keicho: Based on what I found out,
dio’s goal was to scour the globe
in search of potential stand users,
and somehow he discovered
my dad had the capacity to manifest a stand.
However, to this day,
i have no idea what the nature of his stand is.
And then things changed again.
It’s been ten years, but I remember it like yesterday.
It was 2:00 in the afternoon.
i’d just come home from a long day at school.
( Okuyasu crying )
Young keicho: Okayasu!
Did that bastard hit you again?
What’s wrong with him?
Okuyasu: No. He didn’t.
Keicho: Huh?
( Mr. Nijimura groaning )
Dio. Dio is dead.
( Groaning )
That must be the reason.
Keicho: Dad?
( Mr. Nijimura screams )
( Okuyasu screams )
keicho: Dad? I’ll call an ambulance.
mr. Nijimura: It’s no use. I’m not sick.
The flesh bud is ravaging my body!
- This is the end! - Keicho: Dad!
after a year, he didn’t know who we were.
The man had forgotten all about his own children
and had become a muttering glob of flesh.
( Mr. Nijimura moans )
Keicho: Dio used to implant his own cells
into the minds of those he distrusted
so he could manipulate his victims
in whatever way he saw fit.
And as you can guess,
he implanted one of those things into dad.
- ( Both gasp ) - ( Mr. Nijimura groans )
Keicho: For ten years, I threw myself into research.
I studied stands. I learned about jotaro.
in my studies, I learned of enyaba the hag
and obtained possession of the bow and arrow.
But in the process, I slowly resigned myself to the fact
that dad would never recover from the curse that plagued him.
My father had already become one with the immortal cells of dio.
Now he spends his days doing nothing but this.
It’s infuriating to watch.
Every moment of every day, for the past ten years,
he’s scratched around that stupid box of rubbish.
If I confiscate it, he wails and groans for days on end.
I’m sick of dealing with it.
Look at his putrid face.
Makes me disgusted with the very idea of life itself.
( Mr. Nijimura squeals )
Keicho: I’ve told you over and over,
stop making a mess!
( Mr. Nijimura wails )
Keicho: Though i’ve noticed, when I discipline the bastard,
he seems to hear me!
Yet he keeps rummaging in his own filth!
but I guess the swine can’t help it!
- ( Koichi groans ) - ( Kicking continues )
Josuke: Enough! You’re the one who needs to stop!
He’s still your father, isn’t he?!
( Keicho sighs ) Yeah, you’re right.
This man is my father, but in blood only.
The detestable thing I see before me
isn’t the father I used to know.
This man sold his soul to dio
and is living the life he created.
But i’m not totally without a heart.
Seeing my one and only father like this is unbearable.
You don’t know how it feels.
All I want to do is end his life
and finally free him from this suffering.
And by putting him out of his misery,
i’ll be able to live my life again.
( Josuke gasps )
Keicho: What did I say?
i’ve had just about enough of you!
Get out of the box right now!
( Mr. Nijimura wails )
Josuke: Hey! You’ve more than made your point!
Keicho: Sorry, but I just can’t let you have this bow and arrow,
not now or ever!
Josuke: That works for me.
i’ll just take that bow and arrow later.
But right now,
my sights are set on that box!
( Shining diamond yells )
- keicho: Huh? - Koichi: Wait. The box?
( Mr. Nijimura groans )
♪
( Keicho gasps )
Josuke: It was clear from the way
he was clutching those scraps of paper
that there was something important about them.
( Mr. Nijimura weeping )
Josuke: Now it makes sense.
( Wailing )
( Keicho gasps )
Koichi: A family photo.
H-he knew what he was doing.
He hasn’t been mindlessly rummaging through that box
for ten years. He’s had a purpose.
He was looking for the photo of his sons when they were young.
It’s true that he’s
not completely aware of his surroundings,
but deep down, his memories are still intact,
memories of better days.
( Okuyasu gasping )
( Mr. Nijimura sobbing )
( Josuke sighs )
Give up on looking for a stand that kills,
because if you focus on using one that heals instead,
then i’m willing to help you.
- ( Nijimura brothers gasp ) - ( Koichi sighs )
Josuke: But first you’ll have to hand over that bow and arrow,
’cause they’re history.
( Keicho sighs )
( Josuke gasps )
You’re not planning to run, are you?
( Keicho growls )
Okuyasu: Bro, please. Enough is enough.
Keicho: Okuyasu.
Okuyasu: Come on. Let’s end this already.
There’s no point in fighting him, right?
Josuke: So, you stuck around.
Okuyasu: What do you say?
there’s a chance dad could get better, couldn’t he?
♪
So what if he doesn’t look the way he used to?
that stuff doesn’t really matter.
The important thing is he’d have his memories and soul, right?
( Keicho gasps )
( Groans ) Okuyasu...
The hell do you think you’re doing?
( Okuyasu gasps ) Bro.
Keicho: Move it, okuyasu!
Don’t you see? It’s far too late
for me to just turn my back on the mission!
I’ve already slaughtered countless people in this town
with the very bow and arrow you’re gripping!
( Okuyasu sputters )
keicho: Besides, as far as i’m concerned,
you’re no longer my brother.
As such, I have no qualms about killing you where you stand.
( Okuyasu gasps ) B-bro.
( Josuke gasps )
Question, is there anyone else living here
besides you two and your dad?
- ( Keicho and koichi gasp ) - Okuyasu: Others?
No, it’s just the three of us.
( Electricity crackling )
Okuyasu: Th-that’s...
Josuke: It’s coming from the outlet.
- ( Stand yells ) - Keicho: Okuyasu!
pull your head out of your ass, you idiot!
( Okuyasu groans )
Okuyasu: No! Big bro!
( Keicho gagging )
Stand: I’ll be relieving you
of this bow and arrow, keicho nijimura!
You do still remember me, don’t you?
Since you awakened my stand when you shot me with this arrow!
( Keicho groans ) I do,
and you are an idiot.
You can’t handle the bow and arrow.
Stand: Keicho nijimura,
stands are a manifestation of the soul.
i’ve matured since you told me that.
but let me guess. You weren’t expecting my stand,
chili pepper, to evolve to this degree!
Keicho: Worse company, atta--
chili pepper: No more words!
( Okuyasu gasps ) Josuke: Hey, is that...
Koichi: Electricity!
Okuyasu’s brother is turning into it,
and so is the bow and arrow!
Okuyasu: Bro!
Don’t touch me!
Y-you’ll get sucked in, too!
( Okuyasu gasps ) Big bro.
Keicho: This isn’t good.
All that work, and he’s stealing the bow and arrow!
( Groans ) Okuyasu...
I knew you’d find a way to screw me over.
- ( Okuyasu gasps ) - ( Keicho screams )
Okuyasu: Big bro!
♪
Koichi: Josuke!
( Josuke gasps ) There’s no doubt in my mind
that a stand user was watching us from that window.
Did you recognize that stand back there, okuyasu?
Okuyasu: I didn’t.
bro was the one who found the stand users,
and when he did, he didn’t tell me a lot about them.
( Gasps )
J-josuke!
Look! It’s...
♪
( Josuke gasps )
( Okuyasu shudders )
Josuke: Okuyasu.
Okuyasu: Bro...
I knew it was only a matter of time before this happened.
I knew all the bad things he did in his life
would catch up to him one day, but still...
In the end, my brother--
my brother used his dying moments
to save my life, didn’t he?!
Josuke, you saw it, right?!
Josuke: Yeah. I couldn’t have said it better.
whatever his faults, your brother saved your life.
( Okuyasu gasps )
( Mr. Nijimura grunting )
( Slurred ) Pagii.
( Telephone rings )
( Ring )
( Receiver rattles )
man: Would this happen to be jotaro kujo?
Jotaro: I don’t recognize your voice.
who is this, and what do you want from me?
Man: The who doesn’t matter, jotaro kujo,
but as for what I want,
i’m kindly asking you to get the hell out of morioh.
Jotaro: Now let me see if i’ve got this straight.
A complete stranger calls
and wants me to just up and leave town.
what would you do if the situation was reversed?
man: Doesn’t matter, since I have the bow and arrow.
- ( Jotaro gasps ) - Man: That’s right.
I took it from keicho nijimura after I killed him,
and I don’t mind getting rid of you either.
i’ve heard all about you, jotaro,
that you have the ability
to stop time for one or two seconds,
but since you’re such a tough guy,
I thought i’d take a shot
at convincing you over the phone first.
Jotaro: Are you a stand user, too?
What do you want with the bow and arrow?
man: I don’t mean to cause you any trouble,
if that’s what you’re implying,
and as long as josuke higashikata
minds his own business,
I won’t lay a finger on him, either.
i haven’t had this stand ability for too long,
so my only priority right now is to have a little fun.
i’ve had enough of dealing with mundane things
like entrance exams and resumes.
Jotaro: So you’re a student, huh?
( Man sputters ) What difference does that make?!
listen! If you wear out your welcome,
i’ll kill you and josuke in ways that’ll haunt your...
Jotaro: How many other stand users
are there in this tow--
( grunts )
( Man laughing )
( Laughter echoes )
( Jotaro sighs )
Here we go again.
narrator: Keicho nijimura was buried
in kunimi peak cemetery, west of morioh.
However, the bow and arrow remains missing.
For okuyasu nijimura, it was time to step up
and look after his father for a while, and...
( Josuke sighs )
( Doorbell rings )
Tomoko: Josuke, can you get that?!
( Josuke groans )
Good morning.
( Gasps )
Okuyasu: Hey, josuke!
Time to go to school, buddy.
- Josuke: Huh? - ( Okuyasu laughs )
Starting today, the two of us
are gonna be going to the same school.
Josuke: Even so, that doesn’t mean
you have to come and get me. This isn’t elementary school.
Okuyasu: No way. You know, I never realized your house
and my house were so close together.
Josuke: Yeah, shocking, but like I said,
you don’t need to walk me to sch--
okuyasu: Come on. You don’t want us to be late!
tomoko: Hey there. Are you one of josuke’s friends?
okuyasu: Hi! I’m okuyasu nijimura!
- Josuke: Huh? - Tomoko: Come on in,
and have some coffee while he finishes getting ready.
Okuyasu: Wow! Really? Don’t mind if I do!
( Chuckling )
have you noticed that your mom’s kinda hot?
I’m right behind you!
Josuke: A comedian. Just great.
What have I done?
♪
♪ Anytime I need to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes, and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight, and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in, and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, i’d die to find out ♪