Tomoko: For the love of--josuke!
Are you still playing that game?
- ( Video game playing )
- If you don’t turn it off
right this second,
i’m gonna scream!
jotaro:
Five more minutes, please?!
Just five more minutes!
come on, mom.
Just this once!
I can’t stop now!
I’m about to get
to the best part!
Quitting guarantees i’ll live
the pathetic life of a scrub
who doesn’t follow through
on his promises!
Tomoko: Have it your way.
the longer
you play your little game,
the harder these kicks
are gonna get!
- josuke: ...I don’t.
- Tomoko: How long do you think
- you can hold out?
- ( Josuke wails )
I-it’s over.
Shit.
Tomoko: Put it away,
and start your homework.
Oh, and would it kill you
to take off your uniform?
It is nighttime, you know.
( Jotaro sighs )
woman: Sorry.
I can’t see you anymore.
- jotaro: Huh?
- Man: But why, sachiko?
have the flames
of our love burned out?
Jotaro: What’s going on?
I’m pretty sure
that I turned it off.
Ah, come on.
Shut off, will you?
chili pepper:
It would seem jotaro kujo
has refused to leave town,
and after I went out of my way
to give him
an explicit warning.
There has to be a reason,
right, josuke higashikata?
Josuke: I know you.
You’re chili pepper!
♪
( Gasps )
What are you doing here?
Chili pepper: You’re not
the brightest bulb, are you?
Clearly it escaped your notice
that i’ve been popping in and
out of here for a while now.
Josuke: What?!
This asshole’s been keeping tabs
on me the entire time?
( Chili pepper laughs )
One of my other hot spots
is the house
belonging to okuyasu,
the brother of that fool
i knocked off.
I’m also well aware of that
schoolgirl, yukako yamagishi,
and koichi hirose’s reverb,
and I know toshikazu hazamada
and tamami kobayashi
are in the hospital.
Josuke: Something about this
isn’t making sense.
From everything i’ve seen,
you’re a conniving,
birdbrained coward.
What reason could you possibly
have for turning up at my house
ready to take me on
fair and square?
Surely you’re not moronic enough
to believe
that anything you could do
would actually be enough
to mess me up?
Chili pepper: Me, mess you up?
No, nothing so foul
for this birdie.
Your death will be a humane one.
( Josuke scoffs )
So you’re a coward
and a comedian
with a crappy sense of humor.
You’re two for two, birdbrain.
( Chili pepper laughs )
Full disclosure before we begin.
I’ve already told jotaro
his star platinum
poses a great threat to me.
his vigilance
is annoyingly steadfast,
and his stand’s time-stopping
ability is formidable,
so the only course of action
left to me
is to completely decimate
that interloper
in a head-to-head battle
for supremacy.
But before I fight jotaro,
I want to test my abilities
against you,
josuke higashikata.
Why don’t you come
a little bit closer?
i won’t bite.
All i’m asking you to do
is unleash an attack
as swift and precise
as one of star platinum’s.
It’s as simple as that!
and if you’re
all the way back there,
i’m worried your punches
won’t be quite up to snuff.
Josuke: Is that mockery
i’m detecting in your voice?
chili pepper:
No, not in the slightest.
I just have every confidence
in the capabilities
of you and your stand,
so why don’t you come closer?
I want you to give me
your best shot,
so put your back into it, boy.
Here. Come on. Lay one on me.
Make sure to get nice and close.
( Groans )
Incredible! So fast!
how in the--
josuke: I’m tired
of your incessant squawking!
( Shining diamond yelling )
Chili pepper: He’s faster
than I ever imagined.
- ( Groans )
- Josuke: If you keep it up,
i’ll just have
to debeak you myself!
( Chili pepper wails )
Josuke: And by the way,
jotaro’s star platinum’s
got nothin’ on me.
Don’t ever forget that.
chili pepper: Damn it.
My arrogance got the best of me,
and I underestimated
his abilities.
( Shining diamond yelling )
Eh? What?
- ( Chili pepper yells )
- ( Josuke groans )
( Yells )
- ( Chili pepper laughs )
- tomoko: Josuke,
what the hell
is going on in there?
Josuke: That blow, it was like
being on the receiving end
of a supercharged
jet-engine blast.
He might actually be stronger
than Mr. Jotaro.
chili pepper:
Very impressive, josuke.
I wasn’t expecting
your shining diamond
to be so robust.
It would appear
that i’m not the only one of us
who’s matured.
Clearly, my time
hasn’t yet arrived.
Until chili pepper is stronger,
vanquishing jotaro
shall remain a far-off fantasy.
( Jotaro sighs ) All he needs
is a source of electricity
to pop out and pulverize us.
what’s worse is he
can control his stand from afar.
Tomoko: Josuke, why did it sound
like 50 tornadoes
flew through here?
josuke: Don’t know.
Maybe you’re hearing things.
( Okuyasu groans ) Damn it!
I just got bit by another bug.
You know, it’s days like today
i wish I was one
of those fancy bug zappers.
( Koichi gasps ) It’s josuke!
Josuke: Hey, guys.
I’m sorry for the wait.
Okuyasu: What the heck
is this all about, josuke?
i mean,
why’d you wanna meet us
all the way out here
in the boondocks?
Wouldn’t tonio’s or that café
have been a much better place
to sit down and talk?
Josuke: I wasn’t the one
who called you guys out here.
It was actually jotaro.
Koichi: Mr. Jotaro?
Wonder what he wants.
Josuke: I’m guessing
it’s about chili pepper.
koichi: What?!
When you say, "chili pepper,"
you don’t mean that horrible
stand, chili pepper, do you?
( Branch cracks )
( Okuyasu panting )
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Okuyasu: So he’s finally back.
- Josuke: Yeah.
In fact, he paid me a visit
at home last night.
Okuyasu: You prick!
Why didn’t you tell me
as soon as it happened?!
Koichi: Okuyasu, he turns into
a completely different person
any time he hears
even the slightest mention
of chili pepper.
But how can you blame him
when he lost his brother
to that stand?
Jotaro: I told josuke
not to say anything.
Discussing this downtown
wasn’t an option.
We’d be surrounded
by electricity.
Koichi: Mr. Jotaro!
Jotaro: I didn’t wanna risk
being spied on,
- so I had us meet here.
- ( Okuyasu growls )
josuke: Okuyasu,
just so you know, chili pepper
grates the ever-lovin’ shit
out of me, too.
That slithery bastard
thinks he can do
whatever he damn well pleases.
He spies on people, eavesdrops,
swipes anything he wants.
( Okuyasu gasps )
Koichi: Wait a minute.
So that’s why I woke up
to my homework being gone
from my desk the other day!
It makes total sense to me now!
And here I thought
my mom threw it away
- when she took out the trash--
- josuke: Do you really think
now’s the time
to worry about that, koichi?!
Look, this is the bottom line.
The only reason chili pepper
hasn’t raised even more hell
is ’cause we’re around,
but don’t let that fool you.
He’s a lot stronger
than he lets on.
He can drag anyone he wants
into the phone lines
as easy as making a prank call.
there’s no doubt
he has the bow and arrow.
Right now, we need to focus
on who he’s shot with it.
i know firsthand
how much stronger he’s gotten.
We have to find
chili pepper’s user
as soon as humanly possible.
Koichi: But how do we do that?
Josuke: Well, we’re here
to figure it out together,
right, Mr. Jotaro?
Jotaro: No, not really,
but we’ve found someone
to do just that,
and the three of you
will be pleased to know
our guest of honor is arriving
at the port of morioh
- at noon today.
- Koichi: Huh?
okuyasu:
Just who is this someone?
Josuke: Hold on!
Is he a stand user?
Jotaro: He is. The name
of his stand is hermit purple,
but he’s gotten way too old to
risk going out into the field.
Fighting as a whole
is out of the question.
josuke: What?
Just how old is this guy?
I mean, you have met him before,
haven’t you?
jotaro: Yeah.
I know him quite well, actually.
he used to be
pretty studly back in the day,
but you wouldn’t know it
looking at him now.
he’s 80--
no, make that 79 years old.
josuke: 79?!
The guy’s practically a fossil!
Jotaro: His legs definitely
aren’t what they used to be,
so he uses a cane,
and two years ago,
he had gallstones removed,
not to mention his cataracts.
All his teeth are fake now,
so he grumbles about missing
his t-bone steaks.
Oh, and he’s going senile, too.
Josuke: Give it a rest.
Next you’re gonna tell me
he likes to talk
to mailboxes. Come on.
You have gotta be
yanking our chains.
Jotaro: The real reason
I had you guys come here
was so that you
could protect the old man.
if chili pepper
gets wind of his arrival,
you can bet he’ll stop
at nothing to take him down.
The thing he dreads most
is one of us discovering
the true identity of his user.
( Josuke sighs )
But that doesn’t explain
how the old-timer
is gonna help us.
Jotaro: I was against it, too,
but as soon as he heard
about the bow and arrow,
he headed to Japan
despite my objections.
Koichi: "To Japan"?
So this person isn’t Japanese,
Mr. Jotaro?
- Jotaro: Correct.
- ( Koichi gasps )
Josuke, this is life-changing!
Josuke: Huh? What is?
What do you mean?
Koichi: Think about it.
He’s a 79-year-old stand user
who isn’t from Japan!
( Josuke gasps ) Hey!
- You can’t mean--
- ( Motorcycle starts )
- Okuyasu: Eh?
- ( Both gasp )
chili pepper:
That’s what I needed to hear.
Okuyasu: Watch out!
It’s chili pepper!
jotaro: Blast it!
How’d he find us way out here?
( Engine revving )
( Chili pepper laughs )
( Koichi gasps ) But how?!
There aren’t any power lines
in this area!
jotaro: He used
the motorcycle battery.
He must have hidden inside it
and come here with okuyasu.
Okuyasu: He hijacked my bike?!
Josuke: And he heard everything!
chili pepper:
So the port of morioh at noon,
that’s where i’ll find
the old fogey of a stand user
who could locate me, eh?
The moment that codger
pulls into port,
i’ll rip him up and continue
my reign of debauchery!
jotaro: Damn it,
he knows about the old man!
in other words,
he knows about josuke’s father.
( All gasp )
At the speed he’s going,
chili pepper’ll
get to the old man
before we can get him to safety.
Koichi: Quick, josuke!
use your stand
to Chuck a rock or something
at that bike and take it down!
Okuyasu: Don’t even
think about it.
That piece of shit is mine.
i’m gonna crush that
murdering jailbird into dust
if it’s the last thing I do!
Koichi: He cut
through space itself!
( Chili pepper gasps ) Damn,
it’s keicho’s little brother!
Okuyasu: What’s the rush?
We have unfinished business.
It’s time for you to disappear!
Huh?
chili pepper:
Well done, boy. Well done.
Teleporting yourself
to the motorcycle
was exceptional,
to say the least,
but you wasted your time.
That adorable scratching motion
you do with the hand
is hardly a match
for chili pepper’s
extraordinary speed,
so as usual,
i’m afraid your efforts
have been all for naught.
Face facts, kid. You’re slow.
okuyasu:
Take another look, dickhead.
When I said i’d make
somethin’ disappear,
I meant the motorcycle.
chili pepper:
He destroyed the front wheel!
( Panting )
Okuyasu: It’s safe to say
you won’t be escaping now.
Josuke: That’s using your head,
okuyasu! Way to go!
Luckily for us, chili pepper
won’t be able to move
very far away
from the motorcycle battery.
And check it out.
The nearest power line
is at least 100 meters away.
We’ve got you cornered
like a rat in a trap.
Koichi: That was a close one.
Jotaro: Hey, stay focused.
He isn’t captured yet.
Don’t forget he can still use
the bike’s battery.
He’ll do whatever it takes to
kill okuyasu and fly the Coop.
( Okuyasu growls )
Jotaro: Let’s head over.
Both: Right!
Chili pepper:
Color me surprised.
I didn’t think you’d go to all
this trouble to avenge keicho.
Okuyasu: I didn’t.
I knew who my bro was.
the other shoe
was gonna drop eventually.
someone was bound
to snuff him out over something.
That’s the thing about crime.
No matter how far
you try to run from it,
it always has a way of
catching up to you in the end.
That’s painfully clear,
even to a sap like me.
( Chili pepper growls )
okuyasu: So now
for the business at hand.
Tell me who your user is
and where he lives.
do that,
and i’ll spare your life,
which is more
than you deserve.
( Chili pepper grunts )
interesting.
If I tell you,
you’ll spare me, huh?
You’re surprisingly composed.
I was positive your bowels
would be burning
with vengeful fury by now!
( Okuyasu growls ) To be honest,
i’m secretly hoping
you won’t give me
the info on your user!
I’m itching to scrape you away,
you glow-in-the-dark shit-head,
so give me a reason!
chili pepper:
There’s the real you!
Thinking you can kill me--
( Laughs )
With that sluggish right hand?
- ( Okuyasu sputters )
- ( Chili pepper laughs )
i don’t know
if I should laugh or yawn,
but either way, you won’t be
putting out my lights today!
Okuyasu: You bastard!
I’ll end you!
chili pepper:
And i’ll make sure you realize
how pathetic your stand is
when compared to the marvel
that is chili pepper!
( Okuyasu gagging )
Chili pepper: Now do you finally
understand how slow you are?
- Josuke: Okuyasu!
- Koichi: Okuyasu!
Chili pepper: Not good!
Here comes jotaro.
I can’t stick around
much longer.
Huh?
How’d he get behind me?
Okuyasu: You’re right
about me being slow,
and I may have missed the Mark,
but I swiped away space,
which gives me
the ability to teleport!
Did you forget about that?!
How do you like that,
you beak-nosed freak?!
( Chili pepper groans )
Okuyasu: I might be wrong,
but it seems like
you’re not as fast as before.
Do you think someone as slow as
you can slip by my next attack?
Koichi: Look, you guys!
chili pepper’s
electric charge is fading!
He’s getting weaker
and weaker by the second!
His stand must be
running out of power!
josuke: Well,
would you look at that?
He actually did it!
Jotaro: Okuyasu,
leave him alive!
We’ll handle him
once we get over there!
You’ve already won! Now
our primary focus needs to be
getting him to tell us
where the bow and arrow are.
( Chili pepper gasping )
You’re right about one thing.
My energy is fading.
Your stand may be
as slow as molasses,
but the ferocity of its attack
is downright bone-chilling.
That being said...
Don’t you want to finish off
your brother’s killer for good?
Try using your head
for a moment.
How can you be certain
i’m not simply pretending
to be frail, okuyasu?
- okuyasu: What?!
- Chili pepper: Who’s to say
i’m not luring jotaro in close
so I can cleave off his head?
Okuyasu: Quit spoutin’ bullshit!
Chili pepper: Fine by me.
So what’ll it be?
Will you do away with me now
or wait for me
to get the drop on jotaro?
Okuyasu: You bastard.
( Gasps ) Hold on a minute.
If you were really
up to something shady,
why would you tell me
your plan?
Had he just kept his beak shut,
he could have easily
played us all.
He would have been
in the perfect position
to take me and jotaro out,
and if that’s the case,
since he basically told me
nothing’s wrong with him,
the chances of him attacking me
are practically zero.
At least, I think they are.
Are you trying to say you
want me to kill you after all?
Chili pepper: I’ll let you
come to your own conclusions.
Okuyasu: This is so confusing!
Is he on his last legs,
or is he lying through his beak,
waiting to attack?
Which one is it?!
( Chili pepper panting )
what’s your answer?
Are you gonna do it or not?
Okuyasu: If this asshole
isn’t really injured,
I have to kill him
right here and now.
But is that the right move?
he could
have something up his sleeve.
( Growls )
Shit! Should I?
jotaro: Okuyasu.
I better get over there.
( Chili pepper chuckles )
last chance.
Make up your mind, okuyasu.
( Chuckling )
( Okuyasu groans )
( Growls )
The hell with it!
i’m putting an end to
this nightmare once and for all!
- It’s time to die!
- Jotaro: Okuyasu!
Okuyasu: Don’t even think
about trying to stop me, jotaro!
He killed my bro! That means he
has to pay the ultimate price!
That’s the only truth
that matters right now,
and my heart has shown me
what I need to do!
Now eat shit, and die,
you glorified night light!
( Chili pepper screams )
Josuke: Well, that’s just great.
Finding the bow and arrow’s
gonna be
a real pain in the ass now!
At least he settled things
with that freak.
jotaro: Hang on.
Something doesn’t feel right.
We need to be careful.
My gut’s telling me chili pepper
is still a threat.
( Okuyasu gasps )
Underground electrical cables?
That bastard!
He faked all that
so i’d expose them!
( Chili pepper laughs )
not quite.
I really was fading.
That motorcycle battery
only holds 12 volts.
a few moments longer,
and I would have been done for.
Okuyasu: You lousy...
( Groaning )
Chili pepper: I must
thank you for reviving me!
( All gasping )
chili pepper:
Poor, simple-minded okuyasu!
If only you’d been a good boy
and controlled yourself
as jotaro instructed,
I would have faded away
with the battery.
I know the location
of every electrical line
running through this town.
my original plan was
to escape into those cables,
but they were too far away
from the motorcycle,
and in the state I was in,
digging them up
was out of the question.
Okuyasu: Why won’t you die?!
- He’s faster than before!
- Chili pepper: Hah!
With this much electricity
at my disposal,
I have more than enough power
to challenge
your lackluster right hand!
( Okuyasu yells )
( Screaming )
Koichi: Okuyasu!
Chili pepper: I seem to remember
your brother keicho
saying something about you
never failing to hold him back.
Ah, how right he was!
Your soul is underdeveloped.
( Laughs ) Revenge was never
going to be within your reach,
you cocksure ignoramus!
So long, jotaro and josuke.
I’m taking off,
but not before I find
that old coot, Joseph joestar,
and see to it
that he shares the same fate
as the lamentable
nijimura brothers!
To the Victor go the spoils!
Koichi: Okuyasu, no!
( Okuyasu screams )
( Koichi whimpering )
He pulled him into the cables.
Okuyasu! Okuyasu!
Jotaro: Good grief.
To think we were that close,
and he still got away.
josuke: That stand
was absolutely terrifying.
how do you even
begin to fight a remote stand
- with boundless power...
- koichi: What?!
what the hell
are you guys talking about?!
okuyasu was--
he was murdered in cold blood,
and you’re rambling
about how strong the enemy was?!
Jotaro: Oh, yeah. You’re right.
We should check up on okuyasu.
Josuke: Leave it to me.
Jotaro: There’s one consolation
in all this.
He must’ve had a guardian angel
lookin’ out for him.
Josuke: Weird as it sounds,
his right arm
getting chopped off
was the best thing
that could have happened.
Koichi: Huh?
Josuke: Let’s go,
shining diamond!
You don’t have to worry,
so dry those tears, koichi.
Once I fix his arm,
his body’ll come back.
( Okuyasu screams )
Chili pepper: What the hell?!
Koichi: All right!
I thought we’d lost you
for good, okuyasu!
( Okuyasu panting ) Shit.
I-I was totally outclassed
by that bastard.
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Koichi: It’s not about revenge,
and we can’t focus on setbacks.
joseph joestar,
he’s the priority here.
He needs us. I know it’s tough,
but that’s how we’re
gonna beat chili pepper
and get true justice.
You have to do this
for our town,
and if that isn’t enough,
then do it for all the people
you care about.
Josuke: I might be
stating the obvious,
but this isn’t good. Guess I
was taking this too lightly.
Jotaro: Yeah. We have
to reach the old man’s boat
before chili pepper.
Let’s head to the port.
Koichi: How can you be so
nonchalant at a time like this?!
look at okuyasu!
He’s still in shock over here!
Josuke: We can get to the port
faster this way.
Jotaro: Sounds good.
Koichi: Would you guys
wait for us?!
okuyasu:
There’s no way around it.
bro, in order
to beat chili pepper,
I have to surpass you.
Sailor: Mr. Joestar,
we’ll be arriving
at the port of morioh
any moment now.
( Joseph coughs )
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪