♪
Rohan: Hmm? Who is this?
I’ve never seen him before.
Kinoto: Good afternoon, sir.
I’m kinoto,
the architect you spoke
on the phone with earlier today.
I’m here to assess the fire
restoration and renovation.
Rohan: Oh. Yeah, that’s right.
We did agree to meet.
Kinoto: Huh?
Rohan: Heaven’s door, attack!
( Kinoto groans )
Rohan: My apologies
for the forceful greeting,
but one has to be cautious.
I see. Born in 1970.
Top-notch architect.
Name, masazo kinoto.
he’s definitely
the one I called for repairs,
and he doesn’t seem
to be a threat.
Hmm?
That’s peculiar.
Then again, no one’s without
their bizarre fears and phobias.
At any rate, he seems safe
enough to let into the house,
though that rosham-brat
also seemed innocent.
a simple command
of "I can’t attack Rohan"
- should suffice for now.
- ( Writing )
Kinoto: Huh?
Oh, my. I’m so sorry.
Did I just make a faux pas?
Rohan: Not at all.
Come in, and we’ll talk.
We have a lot to discuss.
Huh?
♪
Is something the matter?
Most of the damage is in here.
You can’t perform a proper
assessment from out there.
Kinoto: Oh, no.
Please go on ahead.
I’ll be right behind you, sir.
Rohan: Huh?
( Kinoto grunting )
Now, where is that room?
I’d love to see it.
( Kinoto chuckles )
( Metal clangs )
Toyohiro: I didn’t think
my escape would go so smoothly.
Though I shouldn’t be surprised.
You haven’t even caught
yoshikage Kira yet, have you?
( Both growl )
toyohiro:
Did it ever cross your mind
that my name might be fake
or that I could maybe
be wearing a mask?
Does the name "kanedaichi"
sound real?
Okuyasu: What?
This guy’s a fake?
Josuke: So you’ve be wearing
a gaudy mask all along?
Toyohiro: Leaving this place
has been my mission.
Did you really think i’d
do it without a clean escape?
See you, boys, and I definitely
wouldn’t wanna be you.
Josuke: Hey! Get back here!
Mikitaka: No, Mr. Josuke!
- Don’t come in here!
- ( Both gasp )
Mikitaka: I shall remain
in the tower for now.
Josuke: Yeah, right!
there’s no way
we’re leaving you in there!
Mikitaka: We’re only
in this situation
because I discovered the tower.
as for this,
it’s my fault for deciding
to turn into the power line
and climb up here.
I only wanted to be useful.
I wanted to change your opinion
and for you to be proud of me.
i should have
just listened to okuyasu.
I should have stayed out of it.
( Okuyasu gasps )
mikitaka:
Don’t trouble yourselves.
i am used
to the inside a spaceship,
so this is really quite nice.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Toyohiro: You’re a weird one,
but you’ve got a lion’s heart.
though, to be frank,
I honestly don’t give a damn
who remains trapped in here.
As long as I walk free,
i’m a happy man.
What you fools do
after that is--
josuke: Oh, no.
You’re a permanent resident!
I remember you saying something
about not wanting to be us.
Josuke: Well, once i’m done,
nobody in their right mind
will wanna be you!
Mikitaka: What? Why, josuke?
Toyohiro: Piss off!
Josuke: Thanks to you
cutting this line,
I was able to fix it
and get myself up here.
( Toyohiro gasps ) Damn you.
josuke: Mikitaka,
give me about ten seconds,
and i’ll have you free.
After I put this bro-hole
back in his douche cage,
i’ll heal you up, and it’ll
be like this never happened.
Okuyasu: Be careful up there,
josuke! Don’t you fall!
Josuke: Yeah, as if.
Toyohiro: Props, friend.
mending the wire
to swing up here was ingenious,
but coming back to this tower
was not the smartest move
you could have made.
I would have been
perfectly content
leaving this place behind.
In fact, killing
you pigheaded boobs
never crossed my mind,
but you just had to go
and force my hand!
so now,
for me to make my getaway,
i have no other choice
but to push you to your death!
Josuke: Go to hell!
Shining diamond: Dora!
( Yelling )
( Josuke gasps )
( Gasping )
Toyohiro: You know,
now that I see
your shining diamond up close,
it’s actually
pretty damn impressive.
Even so, you can’t really think
you stand a chance against me.
I could prance around the top of
this tower with my eyes closed.
And i’m guessing your stand’s
range is about two meters.
( Chuckles )
( Grunts )
( Josuke gasps )
( Toyohiro laughing )
( Josuke gasps ) What the hell?!
screw you, dick!
You’re gonna pay for that!
( Toyohiro laughs )
( Mikitaka gasps ) Mr. Josuke!
You have to move now!
He’s already slashed
the tower with his knife!
Look! He carved slits
into the beam!
- Shining diamond: Dora!
- toyohiro: Hmm?
josuke: That was
a real low blow. You know that?
though, to be fair,
as fast as your attacks are,
my shining diamond
won’t even break a sweat.
( Toyohiro chuckles )
Josuke: Keep smirking, freak!
We’ll see if you’re
still wearing that smile
after the ass-whupping
i’m about to give you!
toyohiro: I know
every centimeter of this tower
like the back of my hand,
you loudmouthed shit.
I also know precisely
which angle to cut
to send the projectile
in the direction I desire.
Like a pool shark who’s bored
with his own mastery
of the game,
I know all the moves!
Mikitaka: Pool shark?
- ( Josuke groans )
- ( Mikitaka gasps )
Okuyasu: Josuke, no!
Toyohiro: Didn’t you
just say my attacks
weren’t fast enough to make
shining diamond break a sweat?
Let’s see if that holds true
if you don’t know
where they’re coming from.
Now, how many shots
did I fire back there?
They’re ricocheting
off the beams as I speak.
watch out!
They’re coming for you!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Mikitaka: Mr. Josuke!
behind you!
Mr. Josuke!
( Josuke groans )
Toyohiro: Didn’t I tell you
coming up here was a dumb move?
especially after
your alien friend had the balls
to say he’d stay behind
and cover your ass.
if only you’d
have listened to him,
at the very least,
you could have lived.
( Josuke groans )
mikitaka: No,
not both of his arms.
There’s no way he can dodge
another onslaught.
Toyohiro: Now the time’s come
for the finishing blow!
- I think i’ll aim for...
- Josuke: Hey, okuyasu,
question for you.
you saw this guy’s
projectile thingies, right?
did you catch
how many of ’em I knocked away
with my shining diamond?
I’m cooking up something.
okuyasu: Huh?
Yeah, saw the whole thing.
You definitely managed
to land a hit
on four of those suckers.
Toyohiro: How the hell
can you be so nonchalant?
Josuke: Four of them, huh?
Well, that should be plenty.
I only need four shots
to take you down.
Toyohiro: What are you
blathering on about?
Josuke: If i’m
remembering right,
you used the word "ricochet."
yeah, that’s right.
You said your stand’s energy
ricocheted around
like billiard balls.
well, that is
what you said, isn’t it?
that’s right!
What are you gonna do about it?!
Josuke: By now,
you know my stand
is called shining diamond,
but did the old fart
in the photo
let you in on the fact
that it can correct
destroyed matter
and fractured energy?
Toyohiro: Maybe he did,
maybe he didn’t,
but what’s that got to do
with your current predicament?
Are you really telling me
you had the time
to correct something just now?
What kind of fool
do you take me for?!
( Groans )
mikitaka:
He corrected the energy
ricocheting between the beams
so that it would return
to the slashed steel.
Mr. Josuke, I thought
that you were done for,
but you had already won
this battle.
toyohiro:
How’d you pull that off?
josuke: You said
coming up here was a dumb move.
What do you think
of my plan now?
( Toyohiro screams )
Please forgive me.
The whole reason
i started living
in this godforsaken tower
was to get away
from other people.
But that cranky, old grand-dude
in the photograph
convinced me
to trap a stand user.
He said if I could just do that,
he’d make sure
i’d be able to have a life
in the outside world,
so I decided to go for it.
Please, go easy on me!
I’m begging you!
If you’d let me go back
inside the safety of my tower,
i’ll be a good boy!
I never wanna leave home again!
Just let me stay
between these beams.
I promise i’ll live out the rest
of my life in peace and quiet.
Narrator: New morioh landmark,
the man in the electrical tower.
He’s a marvel
of self-sufficiency,
but if you bring him
a bit of salt or snacks,
he’ll be happy
to let you take a picture,
but don’t expect him to be
able to muster up the courage
to take off his mask
or divulge his real name.
Josuke: Yeah, that’s fine,
but tell us more
about the old guy.
Did he tell you anything else,
like the whereabouts of his son,
yoshikage Kira?
Anything would help us.
( Toyohiro sighs )
well, actually,
he did mention a stand user.
- I think his name was koichi.
- ( Both gasp )
josuke: What else
do you know about koichi?!
Toyohiro: Hey,
take it easy, man.
The geezer and I were just
having some casual conversation.
He barely even mentioned him.
The subject never came up again,
so I didn’t think
to ask anything,
and he didn’t elaborate
on who the guy was.
Okuyasu: Get to the point!
What did he say about koichi?
Toyohiro: Well, he told me that
he found a way to eliminate him.
( All gasp )
Josuke: He said
he got rid of him?!
toyohiro: And if
his son’s yoshikage Kira,
then it seems like the old man
might have already
caught up to him.
He said, from now on,
he would do more
than just protect his son.
He’d start seeking out
and attacking his enemies.
then he told me that
a recently created stand user
eliminated a user named koichi
just this morning.
But that’s all. I swear.
( All gasp )
Kinoto: Hmm,
and this would be--
( yelps ) Goodness!
Look at this door.
this will be
about 800,000 yen by itself!
And these designs are from
the victorian or edwardian era,
and they even use
English-made materials.
This is going to be a doozy.
Rohan: So he doesn’t want
anyone looking at his back.
I suppose that could explain
his rather odd behavior
when he first arrived.
Here you go.
Kinoto: Oh, thank you.
Rohan: Before it gets cold.
( Kinoto laughs )
Oh, i’ll be fine.
( Rohan sighs )
♪
( Kira gasps )
Now’s not the time.
I must resist.
( Fingernails rustle )
♪
Toyohiro: Boy, I really hope
that they find koichi
safe and sound.
Mikitaka: Hmm.
( Okuyasu panting )
( Growls )
Come on! I can’t find him
at home or at school!
He’s disappeared!
Koichi! Koichi!
Where are you, koichi?!
I’m not giving up,
you hear me?!
I’m gonna do whatever it takes
to find you, koichi!
Josuke: That’s the long
and the short of it.
I wanna know if you’re
willing to get off your ass
and help me find koichi
with your scent-tracking
ability, yuya fungami.
( Yuya growls )
Josuke: If you do,
i’ll get rid of your injuries.
That’s the deal.
Yuya: I’ll say it once,
understand?
Don’t you mess with me, josuke!
I don’t play around,
and I won’t forgive you
for attacking me like a savage
and landing me back in this bed!
What makes you think
i, yuya fungami,
would sacrifice my pride
to help you?
Josuke: So you’re
turning me down, huh?
I kinda figured
this’d be a long shot.
Well, see you.
I’m short on time.
Yuya: Wait. Where are you--
don’t tell me you’re
gonna leave just like that.
Hey, would you wait a sec?
You haven’t even given me
the chance to bargain!
- Okay, fine! Have it your way!
- Josuke: Hmm?
Yuya: I’ll help you
find your little friend.
It’s not like I actually
have a choice in the matter.
I guess I could hold out
for a better bargain,
but then i’d just be stuck
in this dump even longer.
I can’t give my girls the kind
of attention they deserve
while i’m like this,
and, for all I know,
they could be on their way
out of my life forever.
This is so horrible, you know?
And, besides, the accident
that got me into this whole mess
is my own doing.
I’ve got nothing against you.
Now can you hurry up and
get to the healing already?
these injuries
are driving me insane!
Josuke: Quit your complaining.
Shining diamond already
reversed your injuries.
Yuya: Huh?
Um...
♪
Mmm.
There’s that gorgeous face.
I’m a stunningly beautiful
creature, aren’t I?
At the very least, it’s like
i’m one of michelangelo’s
sculptures come to life.
But now that i’m
getting a better look,
I think my eyes
are slightly droopier.
Your stand can actually
fix things 100%, right?
josuke:
Count your blessings, douche!
Now stop preening in the mirror,
and tell me how well
your sense of smell works!
Well, let’s see. I can’t promise
i’d be as good as a trained
hunting dog or anything, but...
( Sniffs ) Hmm.
For example, I can tell
that there are three girls
walking up the hall right now.
It smells like reiko,
akemi, and yoshie.
They’re my fangirls, remember?
Based on their scent,
they’re coming back
from the pachinko place.
- Reiko: Yu-babe, what’s up?
- ( All gasp )
Akemi: Yu, baby, you’re out
of that icky hospital bed!
Yuya: Yo.
Yoshie: Yu, baby, you’re back.
Women: Yu, sweetie!
Yuya: There, there,
everything’s fine, vixens.
- ( Josuke growls )
- ( Women gasp )
Reiko: You’re josuke,
aren’t you?
Akemi: Why the hell
are you here?!
Wanna get skewered
right here and now?
yuya: Easy, girls.
I hold no ill will toward him.
More importantly, you gals just
got back from pachinko, yeah?
reiko: Huh?
How in the world did you know?
Yuya: Because all of your skirts
reek of ass sweat.
Why else would you be planting
those supple cheeks
on vinyl chairs for so long?
say, akemi,
you got any chocolate?
You won at pachinko, didn’t you?
Akemi: Yeah, I did!
You’re amazing, yu.
Here. We brought you a souvenir.
Yuya: Now do you see, josuke?
- (Chuckles )
- ( Women giggle )
I am who I am thanks to these
lovely dames in my arms.
Thanks to you, I can hold them
again, so i’ll help you.
Josuke: You said you weren’t
as good as a hunting dog,
but as far as i’m concerned,
you’re even better!
♪
Kinoto: I’m aware
that the upstairs floor
sustained fire damage as well.
I’ll perform the estimate,
so please go ahead without me.
Rohan: What’s this man doing?
Why’s he so obsessed
with hiding his back?
What’ll happen if I look?
( Kinoto grunting )
( Chuckles )
Rohan: I have to see it!
How could I not want to look
after that display?
If I have to trick him,
then so be it.
Ah, how annoying.
It’s so itchy.
If only there was
some way or other
I could reach this itch.
I suppose it would be
quite rude of me
to ask a person I just met
to scratch it for me, huh?
( Kinoto groans )
I suppose I don’t mind helping.
♪
Josuke: Right.
This is the place.
We found koichi’s bag
lying right here
in the open with no explanation.
His house is only about
two minutes up the road there.
How did this new stand user
storm koichi and snatch him away
from a busy street
first thing in the morning?
Somebody should have seen him.
Yuya: Hmm.
( Sniffing )
Hmm.
Josuke, our little deal doesn’t
include me fighting, does it?
Because when I
agreed to come here,
I was told that i’d
only be used for tracking.
Josuke: Hmm?
Yuya: I won’t feel
comfortable proceeding
until you tell me
I won’t be fighting anyone.
Josuke: Why bring something
like that up at time like this?
Yuya: Because somebody’s
been tailing you.
Josuke: What?
Yuya: It’s that man over there.
( Josuke gasps )
♪
And that’s not all!
I smell koichi’s scent
on that man!
Of course. He must have
something on him
that belongs to koichi!
Josuke: Are you serious?
That’s the guy
we’re looking for?
Hey, you! Come back here!
Tell me what you did
with koichi,
you kidnapping bastard!
( Both gasp )
Jotaro: Mom?
( Gasps )
What the hell?!
It’s definitely mom.
She’s out cold,
but she’s alive.
Yuya: I was watching from here
and still don’t have
a clue what happened.
When did he change
into josuke’s mom?
I heard jotaro can stop time
for a couple seconds,
but this is a new level
of timey-wimey bullshit!
And even jotaro wouldn’t be able
to quickly swap out one person
with another like that!
josuke: If he had
just come out and hit me,
I would’ve been fine
with knocking him out,
grabbing koichi,
and calling it a day,
but that bastard
went after my mom.
scum like him
needs to be punished!
This scheming scumbag
is going down!
hey, yuya! Where’s
that piece of shit hiding?!
I’ll make him pay
for what he’s done!
Yuya: How the hell would I know?
You were touching the guy
and managed to lose him!
wait a sec.
He’s still here, josuke!
i’m still picking up
a trace of his scent nearby!
Man: Hmm. Yuya fungami, eh?
Who knew a simple nose
would be such a nuisance?
I never dreamed these fools
would sniff me out, as it were.
either way,
releasing josuke’s mother
was all part of the plan,
the perfect plan
to observe josuke.
Observation. ( Chuckles )
That’s what my stand,
misterioso, does best.
Misterioso meticulously observed
koichi hirose’s movements,
as well as your mother’s.
♪
( Tomoko growls )
That boy really pisses me off.
I’ll just help myself to his!
Eh? Huh?
♪
That josuke!
So he is home, after all.
Show yourself, kid!
Huh?
( Sighs )
Hmm?
( Gasps )
Man: No one in the world
is immune to fear.
( Tomoko gasps )
Man: You really shouldn’t
hide the glow of fear
or the tremors of dread.
there’s a kind of fear
that lies deep within the soul.
No matter what you do,
it can never be wiped away,
- not ever.
- Tomoko: Who are you?
How did you get into my house?
( Swallows )
Man: According
to my observations,
you tend to swallow your saliva
when gripped with the equalizer
of unyielding fear.
all people exhibit
certain unconscious behaviors
when in a state of panic.
Certain terror-induced quirks
come swirling to the surface.
Did you know about yours?
Tomoko: I don’t know
if you’re a robber or what,
but i’m not giving you
any money, so get the hell out!
man: Do I look
like a common burglar?
I don’t want your money.
in fact,
it feels like
I should be paying you.
- Tomoko: Huh?
- Man: I’m having
quite the exhilarating
morning, you see.
Being the recipient
of so much attention
is such a lovely treat.
the attention you’re
showering me with out of fear
is simply wonderful.
( Tomoko gasping )
( Gasps )
( Swallows )
Man: Oh, my.
it looks like
you just swallowed again.
( Grunts )
( Tomoko gasping )
( Swallows )
Man: Ah, you see?! I was right!
Yet another swallow!
so that really is
the telltale sign of your fear!
( Tomoko gasps )
Man: And once I discover
your precious Mark of fear,
my misterioso comes alive
and unleashes
its invincible onslaught!
( Tomoko panting )
( Gasps )
Man: Hmph.
( Grunting )
I’ve transformed
tomoko higashikata
and koichi hirose into paper
with hardly any effort.
When I startled koichi
on his way to school,
I discovered his Mark of fear
is a double blink,
an obvious tell.
Josuke: Yuya, for the last time,
where is the scent coming from?!
Man: I imagined, regardless
of josuke’s tough exterior,
plopping his mother
before his eyes
would certainly
stir up pangs of dread.
( Josuke gasps )
Man: Sure enough, there was
josuke’s very own Mark.
When he experiences fear,
he anxiously bites
his lower lip!
The next time josuke
reveals his Mark of fear,
misterioso will eradicate
that do-gooder
once and for all!
Josuke: Hey, yuya, you haven’t
taken your eyes
off my mom, right?
- ( Yuya gasps )
- Josuke: The user,
is it possible
he’s inside her jacket?
i don’t care
what kind of stand it is.
i need to know
what’s inside this pocket!
Man: Oh, is he
gonna bite his lip?!
Come on. Do it!
Josuke: Yuya, answer me!
Is he here or not?!
man: Damn,
fear hasn’t consumed him yet.
Yuya: We’ve been
over this, josuke.
i never promised
to help you fight any enemies.
We only agreed
that i’d track him.
- Josuke: Eh?
- Yuya: Any more,
and i’d be risking my life!
Besides, I only said i’d help
because you healed me.
There’s no way in hell
i’m goin’ down
as that dumbass
who walks right into harm’s way!
Sorry to disappoint you,
but this guy freaks me out!
( Josuke growls )
Then i’ll check for myself.
nothing.
Both pockets are empty,
other than this piece of paper.
( Sighs )
( Yuya gasps )
the scent’s
out of the pocket now.
Could it be? No, you fool.
if you know
what’s good for you,
you’ll keep
that piece of paper closed.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪