♪
Kira: Good morning.
It’s kosaku kawajiri.
i apologize
for the inconvenience,
but i’ll be arriving
at the office
about 15 minutes late.
My son is misbehaving,
and I must educate him
on the finer points
of familial respect.
yes, I understand.
The matter is inconsequential
from the perspective
of a business owner. Right.
My deepest apologies.
Yes, of course. Thank you, sir.
I’ll handle my son straightaway.
Once that’s done,
i’ll head to the office.
Yes, sir. Got it.
thank you
for your understanding.
- ( Line hangs up )
- ( Scoffs )
Damn kosaku kawajiri.
What an obsequious little drip.
you were just
a socially anxious nitwit.
Why would you want to climb
the corporate ladder?
Josuke thinks he’s so clever.
It’s clear that he only hid
inside that house
because he thinks
he’ll have the advantage
in a close-combat battle.
Admittedly, there’s a kernel
of truth in that belief.
If I want to survive
this skirmish,
i’d be wise to avoid
shining diamond like the plague.
If I can pinpoint
josuke’s location,
i can launch
an air bullet from here
and possibly make contact.
All right.
- Man: Hey, you!
- Kira: Hmm?
Man: This is private property.
why are you
creepin’ around here?
( Kira sighs )
Man: What’s that
supposed to mean?
You tryin’ to say
you ain’t trespassing?
Okay, then I have some questions
for you, smartass!
Kira: Is this your house?
How long have you been watching?
Man: Just a minute. I’m askin’
the questions around here!
And I happen to live next door!
I was takin’ a nap,
but someone started
makin’ a damn commotion
and woke me up!
I’ve got my eye on you, creeper!
Lovely rio lives here,
and she said someone
keeps stealing her underwear,
and it just so happens
no one’s home now, perv!
Kira: It must be nice.
Man: Huh?
Kira: Having all that free time.
( Man groans )
Hey, you’re walkin’ away?
damn bastard. How dare
you prey on sweet rio like that?
What a smarmy dick. ( Sighs )
( Gasps )
Ohh!
that perverted
panty plunderer is sick!
These silky skivvies must...
Oh! Ohh!
Ohhh! ( Slurps )
( Panting )
Th-they must be rio’s.
( Switch clicks )
Oh, boy.
Such pure, pristine panties.
It’s my lucky day!
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
- ( rattling )
- ( Hayato gasping )
Crap! It’s no use!
The phone line’s been cut!
( Josuke gasping )
Okuyasu’s dead.
( Hayato sighs )
josuke:
Which leaves me no choice.
I’m gonna use shining diamond
to wipe yoshikage Kira
off the planet.
He’s plagued us long enough.
I’m putting an end to this evil.
- Hayato...
- Hayato: Huh?
Josuke: Hide against the wall
’til this is over.
I don’t want Kira
laying eyes on you.
♪
Now, which way...
which direction
is he gonna attack from?
( Hayato panting )
Huh?
Wh-what?
Hey, look out!
( Josuke gasps )
Hayato: It’s an air bullet,
and it’s moving
right towards you!
Get outta the way!
It’s about the same size
as the one from before.
B-but I don’t get it.
How in the world was he
able to track you down
from all the way out there?!
This doesn’t make any sense!
Josuke: Freakin’ great.
Kira: I see you,
josuke higashikata.
I know the exact distance
between us.
Three meters until impact.
( Hayato gasps )
( Gasps ) There’s the culprit,
and if I can see it now,
that means josuke can, too!
Yes! Now you can dodge it!
No matter how many
of those he shoots,
you can get out of the way!
( Both gasp )
Josuke: What the hell?
hayato: Wait.
Is it able to trace josuke?!
♪
josuke:
That hand-hoardin’ killer’s
found a way
to track my movement.
Where is he? How can he see me?
Hayato: Hey, that room
doesn’t have any windows,
and where there are windows,
the curtains are drawn!
There’s no way he could
have seen you from outside!
it must be automated.
It’s following you on autopilot!
Josuke: No, I don’t think so.
Deadly queen already
has a homing device.
it’s an annoying little
heat-seeker called heart attack.
Just look. This bullet
is completely ignoring
the lit cigarette.
I don’t know all the details,
but i’m willing to bet
if it was a homing device,
the air bullet
couldn’t penetrate the wall.
And think about it.
if this thing
really was automated,
Kira wouldn’t always need
to hit the kill switch himself.
Shit bricks! How the hell does
he know exactly where I am?!
hayato: Hey,
it’s picking up speed!
Josuke: You have to find Kira!
Figure out how the hell
he’s watching me!
Hayato: I found him.
H-he’s right outside the gate.
Kira: Two more meters to go,
and then kaboom.
Josuke: Are you serious?
Hayato: I’m sorry, josuke!
i don’t get
how he’s tracking you
from all the way out there!
Start running!
Josuke: Bastard.
Being a creepy voyeur
is freaky enough.
Kira: One meter to go.
Josuke: But you’ve crossed
into being a stalker
tracking my every move,
and that’s
just a bridge too far.
Shining diamond!
Kira: Contact is imminent!
- detonate!
- ( Switch clicks )
( Hayato screams )
Kira: I finally managed
to get a clean hit.
- ( Glass shatters )
- hmm?
Deadly queen!
Wow, I narrowly escaped death.
But luckily I was prepared.
You’re a true warrior,
and you’ll fight the good fight
to the bitter end.
I know better than to get close
to you, josuke higashikata.
Hayato: J-josuke!
( Josuke groans )
Hayato: Whoa, he’s still alive.
Kira: Hmph. A direct hit,
yet he remains fully intact.
There’s a slight lag when I
manually detonate the bomb,
but its potential
to cause damage is unparalleled.
my next attack
is going to seal the deal.
( Hayato groans ) Please!
I need you to get up now!
we have to find
somewhere safe to hide.
( Josuke groans )
We’re going the wrong direction.
I have to go back.
Hayato: Huh?
We’re going the wrong way.
Turn back!
I have to bash his brains in.
Bring me to that bastard,
yoshikage Kira.
My shining diamond can heal,
but its power won’t work on me.
That said, all the blood I lost
earlier has dried and hardened.
It’s matter like any other.
it’s just
not a part of me anymore.
I can grab a whole bunch of it
and stick it
to whatever I want.
In fact, I trapped some
inside a chunk of glass.
The rain stopped, so that
bloodstain on his jacket
should be good and dry by now.
Behold my wondrous creation!
it’s my own
homemade homing missile.
( Kira gags )
what the hell?
That was the piece of glass
I flicked away earlier.
The blood on my jacket.
( Groans )
the damn glass
was pulled to the blood,
turning into a jagged bullet.
Hayato: Whoa! You got him good!
Your projectile lodged itself
right in his back!
( Josuke gasps )
That’s...
( Kira groans )
his shining diamond is
really starting to irritate me.
that damn stand
is completely unpredictable.
Even so, after my attack,
josuke’s in much worse shape
than me.
One more shot!
Just one more shot,
and yoshikage Kira
will bask in victory!
( Stray cat hisses )
( Hayato screams )
Josuke, it’s here!
And, man, i’ve never
seen him make one this big!
I guess he’s
not messing around.
This has gotta be
his last-ditch attack.
Well, two can play at that game.
Here we go!
Hayato: What are you doing?
The same attack isn’t
gonna work on Kira twice!
You know that! He’ll deflect it!
Josuke: Maybe he will,
but we’ll never know
until we try, right?
By the way, hayato,
i’m sorry to bother you,
but I put that lighter
I was using back in my pocket.
Grab it for me.
I’d do it myself,
but this piece of wood
stuck in my side
is kind of getting in my way.
Hayato: You don’t need
to make smoke anymore!
You can already see
the air bullet, right?!
Josuke: You’ve got it all wrong.
I’m not using the lighter
to see the bullets.
It’s for something else
entirely. Trust me here.
Hayato: Huh?
Josuke: Time’s come.
I have to find out
how he knows where I am.
Stay very still, hayato.
Hayato: Um, josuke?
What the heck are you--
josuke: Hold it
right there, hayato.
( Hayato moaning )
Josuke: I’m starting
to get the feeling
he’s not observing us
with his eyes.
He may be listening
to our every move.
Hayato: Huh?
Josuke: Kira was clutching
a cell phone.
Simple coincidence? Yeah, right.
So who was on the other end
of that call?
His boss from the office? Nah.
There’s only one person
in the world
Kira would call
at a time like this.
( Yoshihiro groans )
( Both yell )
( Yoshihiro gasping )
( Hayato gasping )
Josuke: I’d almost forgotten
about you floating around,
you crusty old man.
Yoshikage kira’s
one and only savior,
his pathetic father.
Hayato: Wow, I had no idea he’d
snuck his way into my pocket.
so that’s it!
Now we have our answer.
( Gasps ) Oh, no!
It’s the air bullet!
it passed
right through the window!
Josuke: Get back!
( Yoshihiro yells )
( Hayato gasps )
It connected!
( Josuke whispering )
i see josuke.
He’s currently fleeing
three meters forward.
( Hayato gasps )
Yoshihiro: Wha?!
I don’t believe it!
Hayato: It completely
bypassed him!
Josuke: Keep going.
Now the fool’s moving
to the right and up,
three meters.
Hayato: He hasn’t figured out
it’s josuke pretending
to be his father!
( Yoshihiro screams )
Josuke: Change of plans.
to the left.
Move one meter. Almost there.
Yoshihiro: What in the hell?!
you are such
a duplicitous dickhead!
Josuke: Bull’s-eye.
Press the button!
- ( Switch clicks )
- Yoshihiro: Yoshikage!
( Koichi gasps )
( Kira laughs )
tell me.
Did that vaporize josuke?
Is he dead?!
Josuke: Yeah, you splattered
the room with him.
( Kira gasps )
Josuke: Now he’s floating
in the great beyond.
But he was already a ghost,
so it’s more
like you shipped him off
to the big nursing home
in the sky.
Kira: Josuke.
J-josuke!
Impossible. This--this has
to be some kind of mistake.
How could this
be happening to me?
I was supposed to live
a peaceful, quiet life
like a flower
in a tranquil field.
suffering like this
was never part of the plan.
I’m yoshikage Kira, damn it!
I can’t lose heart now.
Whatever happens,
I must keep a cool head.
It’s trying times like these
that truly test your mettle.
I know it seems like things
can’t get any worse,
but it’ll all work out,
just like every other time.
even though life
has me backed into a corner,
my wits will turn this bout
of adversity into opportunity.
that is what
yoshikage Kira does.
It’s what he excels at.
This is my world, my reality,
and there’s nothing in my world
that I can’t find
a way to surmount.
( Gasps )
♪
( Panting )
You stepped into my range.
Big mistake, yoshikage Kira,
( Kira panting )
♪
Hayato: I-I can’t believe it.
He took the bait,
and josuke was able to close
the distance between them,
now that it’s
close-quarter combat,
this’ll be over in no time!
Josuke definitely
has the upper hand,
but if Kira
so much as grazes him,
he’ll turn him
into a human bomb!
And if that wasn’t bad enough,
that explosion from earlier
really damaged
josuke’s leg and side.
he shouldn’t even
be able to stand right now.
What are we gonna do?
Kira: That’s enough.
I’m ending you!
Josuke: Then bring it on.
i’m ready.
Now call out deadly queen.
♪
Kira: Deadly queen!
Shining diamond: Dora!
( Kira groans )
Kira: Shit! He’s strong!
( Josuke yells )
Kira: I’m going to die.
this brat is
actually going to kill me!
( Shining diamond yelling )
( Josuke gasps )
Hayato: Wait. What? No way.
When did he do that?
He was so close to winning!
Josuke was totally
overpowering Kira!
Oh, no, was he right?
Could luck really be
on that murderer’s side?
Josuke: What? All that punching,
and I didn’t connect?
Kira: They were blocked
by the air bullets.
But how? I never intended
to use them as protection.
I didn’t have time to act!
- ( Stray cat hisses )
- Kira: Stray cat!
I understand.
Stray cat anticipated
the incoming flurry of blows
and then protected itself
instinctively!
it’s time!
I have to make this work.
once again,
adversity invites opportunity!
Let’s finish them off,
deadly queen!
Make that air bullet a bomb!
Victory!
It’s now an explosive,
and, at this distance,
your death is all but assured!
With the injuries you’ve got,
you don’t have the ability
to avoid my attack.
This is the end for you.
( Josuke gasps )
Damn you, Kira.
Hayato: A contact explosive?!
Josuke! Quick!
You have to grab a piece
of glass or wood to use!
Whack it, and take cover!
kira: I win!
I’ve come out on top,
just like every other time
my back has been
against the wall!
My guardian angel never fails!
Your fate has been sealed, boy!
( Hayato screams )
( Both gasp )
( Kira gasps ) What’s going on?!
Hayato: Check out
the air bullet.
For some reason,
it changed course.
♪
Kira: No, you’re dead.
Hayato: How is he...
Josuke: Is this
really happening?
Josuke and hayato:
Okuyasu, you’re alive!
Okuyasu: Wow, this power,
it always blows my mind.
i’ve thought
about it really hard,
but I still can’t figure out
where the hand puts
all the stuff it scrapes away.
Although, i’ve never been
the best at using my brain,
so I guess
that’s no big surprise.
Off you go.
Kira: How the hell did you...
Hayato: I-it’s okuyasu.
He’s as good as new,
but i’m positive
his heart stopped beating,
and he for sure
wasn’t breathing.
okuyasu: Oh, man,
that dream was freaky as hell.
♪
I was walking around
in this dark, open space
when I suddenly saw
this bright light.
The source of that light
was my brother...
( Chorus vocalizing )
Big bro keicho.
He asked me where I
was planning to go next.
i told him,
"i’m going with you, big bro."
Even as snot-nosed brats,
I could count on my bro.
He made the best decisions,
so I always knew
I was in good hands.
Then he said something
I never expected.
"You have to decide.
"Okuyasu, wherever you go,
you are the master
of your own journey."
I thought about that real hard,
and, as soon as I said
I was going back to morioh,
I woke up in the house.
i had all sorts
of sad feelings, though.
Josuke: Okuyasu.
Hey, news flash, Einstein.
This ain’t the time
to drone on about your bro
and seeing the light!
Okuyasu: Uh-oh. Seems like
someone’s in a shitty mood.
Those injuries
must not be too bad,
since you still have
enough energy to be a dick!
( Josuke groans )
Shut your face!
If you were alive all along,
why didn’t you
open your eyes, dumb-ass?!
Kira: No. Impossible.
Ever since I was a little child,
luck has always been on my side!
I’ve never run out of luck,
and I refuse to start now!
( Stray cat hisses )
Kira: Fire another bomb,
stray cat,
and make it count!
( Stray cat growls )
( Meows )
Kira: Wh-what?!
Okuyasu: Whoa there,
little dude. Easy.
( Hayato gasps ) You did it!
We’ve got Kira now!
Thanks to you,
he won’t be able to use
his air bullets as explosives!
Kira: It makes no sense.
How has it come to this?
♪
Fools! Yoshikage kira’s
never met a problem
he couldn’t conquer!
You won’t do me in!
- Koichi: Mr. Jotaro, look!
- ( Kira gasps )
Koichi: It looks like the bang
came from that house
way over there.
It sounded like some kind
of big gas explosion.
Hey, that man needs help!
Just look. He’s been injured.
- ( Kira panting )
- ( Sirens approaching )
( Gasps )
- ( Okuyasu growls )
- ( Josuke growls )
Koichi: What in the world?
It’s josuke and okuyasu!
Rohan: That kid they’re with,
it’s hayato kawajiri.
jotaro: And the man
bleeding out is kosaku kawajiri.
The puzzle pieces
are falling into place.
Hayato: It doesn’t matter
if you have some guardian angel.
your lucky break is
about to come to a painful end.
Nothing you’ve got compares to
these guys’s righteous hearts!
They’re gonna make you pay!
Can you feel it, yoshikage Kira?
The truth is staring you
right in the face!
You’re nothing compared to them!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Kira gasping )
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪