( Crossing bell ringing )
Narrator: Yukako yamagishi
has been feeling
a bit crestfallen lately.
Girl: You have
a crush on someone?
Girl #2: Yeah, and I think
they like me, too!
Girl #1: Really?!
( Yukako gasps )
Koichi: You’ll never
guess what happened
while I was at angelo’s rock.
- Josuke: Tell us.
- Koichi: These tourists
were taking pictures
and freaking out over it.
( Josuke laughs ) Who knew
it’d be such a hot spot?
( Yukako gasps )
( Koichi sighs )
Josuke: Uh, koichi, you okay?
( Yukako panting )
as long as koichi is
in my heart, that’s all I need.
At least that’s
what I used to think
until the pain set in.
If only he’d look at me.
Even a glance would suffice.
i have no idea
what i’m supposed to do.
( Sighs )
Cinderella?
( Door closes )
( Woman laughs )
This is the best day ever!
I can’t believe
that hunky dreamboat
actually proposed to me!
You’re incredible, Dr. Aya!
thank you so much
for everything! ( Laughing )
( Aya sighs )
Her youth will be spent
as a cheerful troll.
better that
than a doleful beauty.
Oh, the things we endure.
Come in. As you can see,
"our makeover
will help you find true love."
That’s our personal guarantee,
though the choice is yours.
( Car horn honks )
♪
This is beauty institute
cinderella.
Please, don’t be shy.
Yukako: Hmm.
Aya: My name is aya tsuji.
( Sighs ) I’m the principal
owner and aesthetician.
and don’t worry.
I’m not as apathetic as I sound.
( Sighs )
I’m actually very passionate
about my work.
( Sighs )
- Goodness.
- ( Yukako gasps )
aya: You have
such a lovely face, gorgeous.
To think such a striking beauty
was hiding right here
in little ol’ morioh.
Now then, come in,
and have a seat.
First i’ll need you
to fill out a form
with your name and address.
Yukako: Hold on.
I haven’t decided
to go through with
whatever this is.
aya: Of course.
Here’s our list of services.
yukako:
"Marry-a-celebrity makeover"?
Aya: My institute is a bit of
a departure from the mainstream.
You could describe my work
as constructing visages
of good fortune.
( Yukako grunts )
aya: One’s physiognomy,
that is, the form of one’s face,
is what essentially
dictates one’s luck,
which means a face
welcoming of love
increases your chances
of finding love.
- ( Yukako gasps )
- Aya: Hmm.
It’s such a pity.
Your eyes and eyebrows were
cursed with an unlucky shape.
( Sighs )
Yukako: I’ll be
straight with you.
This was the shittiest pitch
i’ve ever heard.
You really charge
for this crap?
Aya: With features
like these, my dear,
the stronger
your affection for a boy,
- the harder he’ll pull back.
- ( Yukako gasps )
Aya: Judging by your face,
we’ve reached
the heart of the matter.
yukako:
You’re what’s the matter.
That has never
happened in my life.
aya: Oh, no?
You’ll have to forgive me, then.
At any rate, let’s dive in.
Pardon the in-between stages.
I haven’t quite mastered
computer graphics.
this is a face
that will find true love.
Yukako: Hang on a second.
Is this for plastic surgery?
Is that what you do here?
aya: No, dear.
I’ll achieve this effect
with only makeup
and a beauty massage.
but be aware
you only have 30 minutes.
If you don’t find love
within that time,
I will refund your thousand yen.
Shall we give it a go?
Aya: Sure, but just the makeup.
i suppose
i’ll humor you this once,
but no funny business.
Aya: Much obliged.
Let’s begin, shall we?
Now please close your eyes.
Don’t spoil the surprise
by peeking, okay?
And whatever you do,
stay perfectly still.
If you start wiggling around,
my hands could slip,
and we don’t want that, do we?
( Thump )
Yukako: Koichi.
Will this really
help me find true love?
i just don’t see
how changing the contours
of my eyes and eyebrows
could alter my chances.
( Koichi panting ) Ahh!
- ( Gasps )
- Yukako: Koichi?
Koichi: I’ve been looking
all over town for you, yukako.
Yukako: Uh, me?
Koichi: Yeah.
Earlier, I saw you
walking past rengatei.
You looked so down in the dumps,
I got a little worried,
and, well, I thought i’d
make sure everything was okay.
yukako: Koichi,
you really went out of your way
just to check on me?
Koichi: Yeah, of course.
i know a lot
has happened between us,
but that’s all
water under the bridge.
I sincerely want you
to be happy.
Yukako: Really?
Do you mean that?
Koichi: Yeah, I do.
Yukako: I can’t believe
this is happening.
Could it be the makeup?
So, uh, koichi...
instead of
just standing around here,
why don’t we find
a quiet place to chat?
Koichi: Huh?
Yukako: If you want.
It’s your decision.
Koichi: You know,
come to think of it,
all that searching
has made me a little thirsty.
Yukako: Huh? Really?!
( Thinking )
It’s actually working.
Things are starting to change.
I’m sharing a table with my
adorable, yet tenacious koichi.
Koichi: Though it’s
not the manliest choice.
( Yukako gasps )
It’s incredibly manly!
i was thinking
about ordering the same thing!
It’s like i’m dreaming.
That physiognomy stuff
works wonders.
I can feel it.
my luck is finally
taking a turn for the better.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Yukako: Ohh.
( Both sighing )
Yukako: Is this
really happening?
I can feel his heartbeat,
the warmth of his body.
this must be
what heaven feels like.
I’ve never been happier
in my entire life.
Man: Oh, look at the time.
It’s already 4:00.
( Koichi screams )
What’s going on?
Why does my stomach feel
like it’s about to explode?!
This isn’t gonna end well!
Sorry, yukako!
I’ve gotta go home right now!
Koichi: No, koichi,
please don’t--
♪
( Flesh creaking )
It’s not fair!
Why does it only last
for a measly 30 minutes?!
( Brakes squeal )
Man: Damn it, lady!
Can’t you see it’s a red light?!
Yukako: Stuff it
up your ass, douche!
it’s not my fault
the frickin’ light turned red!
Why’s it only work
for a measly 30 minutes?!
do something
to make it last longer!
Aya: You found love, didn’t you?
Be happy with that for now.
You can come back
to see me tomorrow.
That’s what my other customers
do in cases like these.
yukako: Never! A fate
that rips me away from koichi
after 30 minutes
is a fate I refuse to endure!
( Aya sighs )
yukako: I want
the win-your-soulmate treatment.
Can you do it?
aya: Graciousness
isn’t your strong suit, is it?
Yukako: Can you do it or not?!
( Aya sighs ) Dear yukako,
cinderella may have
been mistreated,
but found true love, because
she never lost her pure soul.
she’s proof
that fortune favors those
who keep an open mind
and a willing heart.
do you have
the courage to do that?
Yukako: A willing heart?
What does that mean?
Aya: If you truly wish
to transform your luck,
it’ll take more than
mere physiognomic alteration.
( Sighs ) When I was a child,
I loved cinderella’s
fairy godmother so much,
she inspired me
to become an aesthetician.
Like her, i’m dedicating my life
to the service of others
by giving joy.
yukako,
you’re the apple of my eye,
so i’ll help to make
your dream come true.
However, we’ll need to include
more than just your face
in the treatment.
Oh.
♪
( Chuckles )
Yes, only a full-body treatment
will do,
so consider it part of
the win-your-soulmate package.
Use this as an emblem
of the willing heart
that beats within you.
Apply this lipstick
every 30 minutes,
excluding the hours
you’re asleep, of course.
It preserves the potency
of the treatment.
Maintain this ritual,
and you will have the chance
to hold on to your soulmate
for eternity.
It’s 72,000 yen for 24 hours.
Yukako: All right,
let’s just do it.
( Aya giggles )
Very good.
Stay absolutely still,
and be sure
to keep those eyes shut.
♪
Yukako: Called it.
I knew you weren’t
some ordinary beautician.
- ( Aya gasps )
Y-you have powers!
And you can see my cinderella
as well, can’t you?
Yukako: Now I get it.
You’re a stand user like me.
- ( Aya gasps )
- Yukako: But to be honest,
I couldn’t care less about that.
If you were planning
to eliminate me,
you would have done so
a long time ago.
I trust you.
Work your magic,
fairy godmother.
Aya: You startled me there.
Yukako: That’s nice.
Start the treatment.
( Aya sighs )
Such a sublime girl.
let’s begin.
Know that you’re in great hands.
( Clanking )
Cinderella has the ability to
transform the body’s appearance.
its power gives
my win-your-soulmate treatment
that extra kick.
yukako, dear,
bathe in your new beauty,
as you have become
invincible in love.
Koichi: This doesn’t
make any sense.
my stomach
suddenly feels better.
What the heck?!
This is yukako’s bag!
Shoot! I have to hurry
and get it back to her!
( Gasps )
♪
Yukako: Hi, koichi.
Koichi: Y-yukako.
( Shuddering )
Oh, yeah. Before I forget, here.
Guess I must have picked up
your bag by mistake.
( Yukako gasps )
Koichi: This one’s mine.
The whole thing was my fault.
I’m sorry.
Well, see you later.
yukako: Koichi,
please don’t run off just yet!
Look at me.
Koichi: Huh?
Yukako: Really look at me.
Don’t I rouse any special
feeling in you? Any at all?
Koichi: Well, you know,
I think, maybe...
Rohan: Would you look at that?
It’s koichi.
Koichi: Rohan-sensei!
Rohan: I’m heading
over to kameyu
to do a little bit of research.
Do you wanna keep me company?
koichi: I’d like to,
but I really need to head home.
Rohan: I can’t go around
snapping photos at the mall
by myself.
- Yukako: Wait. What went wrong?
- Koichi: Everything’s always...
- yukako: He’s leaving.
- Koichi: About you, isn’t it...
Yukako: Wasn’t I
supposed to become
an invincible heroine of love?!
what happened
to cinderella’s powers?!
Because right now,
this mission is a dud!
ms. Hirose:
Hey there, sweetheart.
Aya: Rest assured.
Koichi has already
fallen madly in love with you,
but his rational mind is
resisting his heart’s impulses.
Did something happen
between you two?
that might be
the source of the problem.
Ms. Hirose: Oh, my!
Is this the manga artist?
It’s wonderful to meet you.
Aya: Everything’s
going to be fine.
Aya: Soon enough, the tables
will turn in your favor.
Cinderella’s power’s absolute.
And so you know,
it’s currently 4:45.
Your 30 minutes
have almost expired.
It’s imperative you remember
to apply the lipstick.
Yukako: I know.
I’m putting it on now.
The tables are gonna turn
in my favor, huh?
josuke: What?
You’re going to kameyu?
Hey, that’s funny. So are we!
yukako: Huh?!
What the hell’s going on?!
It’s like a damn block party.
And to make matters even more
awkward, his mother is here.
"the tables
will turn in your favor."
My ass, they will!
i’ll butcher
that bullshitting beautician!
Rohan: This seems like
an excellent place to start.
( Baby crying )
Rohan: Huh?
Joseph: Sonny, you can’t
use a flash near the baby.
This isn’t good, josuke.
the stress
is triggering her powers,
and she’s disappearing!
( Josuke panting )
Let’s go, old man!
We gotta get outta here!
Joseph: Pardon us.
Coming through.
Josuke: Move it, people!
outta the way!
Ms. Hirose: What’s happening?
( Koichi yelps )
joseph:
Sorry about that, koichi.
( Both gasp )
♪
Koichi: Wowzers. Yukako.
Yukako: K-koichi, i--
she was right.
The tables have turned
in my favor.
Our willing hearts beat as one,
and our souls are intertwined
in a magical dance.
Nothing else matters
but us and this moment.
My new life begins now.
i can feel it.
Josuke, okuyasu, don’t freak,
but yukako and I
kinda made out, so yeah.
( Josuke slurps )
( Yelling )
Run that by me again!
What’d she do to you?!
are you gonna have
to teach her another lesson?!
Koichi: Whoa, take it easy.
You’ve got it all wrong.
She didn’t do anything.
if i’m being honest,
I think i’ve fallen for yukako.
- josuke: Wha?!
- Koichi: She’s grown on me,
and I get excited thinking
about spending time with her.
She makes me feel
all warm and fuzzy.
Could this be love?
josuke: Yo, are you
catchin’ all of this, okuyasu?
This gushy stuff would
shock the pants off a stand.
Those two playing tongue hockey?
- ( Okuyasu crying )
- Josuke: Eh?
Eh?
Pull it together! It’s weird,
but it’s nothing to cry about.
anyway, koichi,
I don’t have the faintest clue
as to what spawned
this stunning change of heart,
but, hey, if you and yukako
are really into each other,
then I wish you both
the best of luck.
koichi: Thanks,
but that’s not the problem.
i don’t know
what’s going on with her,
but she’s refusing to see me.
- both: Huh?
- Koichi: It’s all so baffling.
She’s been absent from school
for two days.
She won’t answer the phone
or say a single word.
She’s off the grid,
but how come?
Okuyasu: Wow, so she went awol
after you guys kissed?
Josuke: And you haven’t
talked to her since?
- Koichi: Not a word.
- Okuyasu: Uh-oh.
The silent treatment’s
a real bad sign.
it’s a shame, too.
I admired her crazy devotion,
but ghosting you like this
is so uncool.
Josuke: It’s gonna
be awkward as hell,
but I think your best bet
is asking yukako
about it face to face.
i’m sorry, bud, but we
shouldn’t get involved in this.
Koichi: Yeah.
Okuyasu: But if
things turn ugly,
give us a holler,
and we’ll rush over.
We’ll be there to help
before you know it.
Koichi: Thanks, guys.
I’ll see you both later.
Josuke: See you.
( Okuyasu crying )
But still, damn that koichi.
Why does he get to kiss a girl?
Josuke: Calm down!
You’re freaking out
over nothing again.
( Koichi gasps )
I’d know that hair anywhere.
Yukako!
( Yukako gasps )
Koichi: Please, wait up!
We need to talk!
( Sighs ) Yukako?
( Yukako shudders )
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Yukako: I’m sorry.
i don’t know
who you’re referring to.
Koichi: Oh, my mistake.
i saw your hair
and thought
you were someone I know.
♪
Hmm?
yukako: No,
I don’t want you to go!
Ohh. Oh, koichi.
( Stifled yelling )
( Shrieks )
Why the hell would you do this
to me, you conniving shrew?!
My face is falling apart,
and your stupid makeup
just cracks and flakes away!
( Aya screams )
( Yukako panting ) Damn you.
You’re a backstabbing bitch!
Turn my face back to normal!
( Aya sighs ) Foolish girl.
Seems you didn’t follow
my instructions.
( Yukako yelps )
It’s such a shame.
I truly thought i’d impressed
upon you the importance
of applying the cinderella
lipstick every 30 minutes.
yukako: So this is
my punishment for forgetting?
( Gasps ) What is this?
My hands, what the hell
is wrong with them?
( Shrieks )
The skin on my hands
is breaking down!
Aya: Your palm lines and
fingerprints are disappearing.
that’s what happens
when you don’t follow orders.
that lipstick was
an assurance of good fortune
during your quest for love.
Tremendous energy is required
to change the course of one’s
destiny, and it’s all used up.
You’ve only yourself to blame
for not taking
your destiny seriously.
Yukako: Hey! Do you wanna die?!
Aya: Die, you say?
Ambition and wealth aren’t
my only motivating factors,
so save the intimidation.
i modeled myself
after the fairy godmother.
She was a sorceress
of the highest level
and bringer of happiness.
It really is such a shame.
It’s clear to me now
that I never should have tried
to make your wish come true.
Your face and palms
are long gone.
They’ve been erased
from this world.
Yukako: What did you say?
Aya: That they’re gone.
and who has use
for things with missing parts?
Yukako: My face,
it’s gone forever?
This isn’t fair.
how am I supposed
to live my life like this?
Koichi: Yukako.
( Yukako gasps )
It’s koichi.
why is he here?
I can’t let him learn my secret.
No, i’m afraid not.
Sorry, but you’ve got
the wrong person.
- Aya: Hmm?
- Yukako: Dr. Aya,
your beauty institute
is for women only, correct?
I want him out of here now.
( Sighs )
Koichi: Nice try,
but you can’t fool me.
I’d know that tough-as-nails
temperament anywhere.
Now I know for sure
you’re yukako.
( Yukako gasps )
koichi: Your personality
leaves a real strong impression.
And this lady,
she’s a stand user.
Is that right?
From what i’m gathering,
she did something to you.
( Yukako gasps ) It’s all over.
I can’t live like this.
You’ll pay for this.
Aya tsuji, i’m gonna murder you!
Aya: Don’t give in to despair.
( Yukako gasps )
( Gasps )
Koichi: What the hell?!
Part of her face flew off
and is flying around the room!
Aya: There we go.
So this is koichi. Hmm.
He saw through
your altered state
and identified you as yukako.
You tried denying yourself
in front of him,
but some people just have
an eye for character.
All right, yukako.
out of consideration
for this young man’s efforts,
i’ll give you one final chance
as a fairy godmother.
Select one of these faces.
You have one chance,
so choose wisely.
Know that your original face
is no more,
but cinderella remembers
the face of each patient
that has made use of its ability
and can replicate them.
Now pick your own face
from among the samples.
If you can find it,
there’s a chance
your original features
could be restored.
your palms
and fingerprints, too.
much like cinderella
and her famous glass slipper,
i invite you
to find your perfect fit.
yukako: Why didn’t you
say that earlier, Dr. Dumbass?!
I’ll be out of here
in no time flat!
I look in the mirror every day,
so how hard can this be?
Aya: Don’t get cocky. If you
choose someone else’s face,
it’ll clash with your own,
as you might have imagined.
actually,
why sugarcoat the truth?
As an authority
on all things beauty,
I can say your face
will become grotesque.
No one will want to look at it.
what’s more,
the contours of your face
will dictate your destiny.
( Yukako panting )
Koichi: Hey, yukako,
be extra careful.
Remember, your face is reversed
when you look in a mirror.
Yukako: Yeah, you’re right.
Aya: Poor girl.
truth is,
none of the faces are correct.
Every one is a fake.
If you can figure that out,
i’ll return your face to normal.
that is
the fairy godmother’s rule.
yukako: Damn it.
The more I look at them,
the more they look like my face.
But this is the one.
It has to be.
No way i’d be able
to forget my own face.
Aya: You sure about that?
Once you try it on,
you’ll know for sure.
( Koichi gasps )
( Yukako panting )
no, i’m wrong.
This isn’t the right face.
I almost missed it,
but my eyes have
more of a slant than these do.
( Gasps ) Which one is it?
I have no idea! What if I
make the wrong decision?!
Aya: Hmm.
♪
What’s wrong?
You have a face to choose,
so get to picking.
Yukako: No, I won’t.
I refuse to choose.
Koichi: But why?
Aya: So what are you saying?
You want to live out your life
without a face?
Yukako: I’m saying
I want koichi to choose.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- ( Aya gasps )
Yukako: That way...
It’ll be a face koichi can love.
I couldn’t care less
what it looks like,
and the amount of luck it has
doesn’t mean a thing to me.
I’ll bear with the outcome
and live a life free of regret.
Koichi: But what if
I get it wrong?
- What’ll you do?!
- Aya: Hmm?
Yukako: I’ll deal with it.
Please, koichi, for me.
( Koichi grunts )
Here. This is it.
I can’t tell you why I chose it.
I guess it’s just intuition.
But if I did mess up
and choose the wrong face--
oh, by the way,
this guy’s my stand, reverb.
Right, so, anyway,
if I screw up,
i want you
to wound reverb’s eyes
- and blind me for life.
- ( Both gasp )
Koichi: I know you said
you wouldn’t have any regrets,
but knowing you like I do now,
you’d secretly get really upset
if I couldn’t see you
just the way you’ve always been.
and, though I
couldn’t see it before,
i’m in love with you.
I couldn’t bear
to see you unhappy.
That’s why the best solution
would be for me
to never see again.
( Aya gasps )
Yukako: Koichi.
Koichi: Here, yukako.
Yukako: Right.
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: Look!
It’s a perfect fit!
Koichi: That’s amazing!
( Yukako laughs ) Koichi!
Koichi: Yeah, we did it, yukako!
Yukako: It’s all ’cause you were
brave enough to choose my face.
aya: To think
he’d sooner blind himself
than witness his beloved
suffer unhappiness.
I figured, as fairy godmother,
i’d bend the rules
and give them a happy ending.
after all,
if I stole the eyesight
of an innocent young man,
what kind of fairy godmother
would I be?
Yukako, dear, young as you are,
you have a keen eye
for finding good men.
Narrator: Beauty institute
cinderella is open for business.
Our makeovers will help you
find true love.