♪
( Koichi sighs )
Done with another
grueling day of school.
Now all I wanna do
is go home and relax.
- huh?
- Hazamada: Huh?
( Yelps ) Koichi! It’s you.
Koichi: Hey, there, hazamada.
Hazamada: Uh, yeah.
Hi. What’s new?
I’m sorry about all the trouble
I gave you the other day.
Koichi: So, uh, have you
completely recovered
from your injuries?
( Hazamada chuckles )
Sort of, I guess.
The doc sent me home
two days ago.
- Uh...
- Koichi: Eh?
Hazamada: Where’s that bastard--
I mean, where’s josuke?
Koichi: He probably
already went home.
You won’t believe it,
but he found
an invisible baby yesterday,
and now they’re bending over
backwards to find its mother.
Hazamada: So the baby
is a stand user?
Koichi: Looks that way.
Apparently the baby
has formed a bond
with josuke’s dad, Mr. Joestar.
In fact, if Mr. Joestar
isn’t nearby at all times,
she turns everything
around her invisible.
Hazamada: Hmm. Does this mean
this Mr. Joestar
is gonna stick around
morioh for a while?
Koichi: Probably.
Hazamada: I see.
Hey, koichi, do you
happen to like manga?
koichi: Manga?
Yeah, guess I like ’em
as much as the next guy.
hazamada: Have you
ever heard of Rohan kishibe?
He draws "pink dark boy."
Koichi: What kind
of question is that?!
i’m one of the biggest
"pink dark boy" fans in Japan!
Hazamada: No way!
You really like it?
Koichi: You’re talking about
the suspense-horror series,
aren’t you?
I’d never get it mixed up
with anything else.
It can get pretty gross
sometimes, but it’s worth it
for the horror aesthetic
and complex characters.
Hazamada: I completely agree!
by the way,
here’s a little secret.
Rohan kishibe actually
lives right here in morioh.
Koichi: What?!
Did I hear you right?
He lives here in morioh?!
It’s almost too good to be true!
Are you sure?!
hazamada: I know!
I couldn’t believe it either!
I heard some realtors
talking about it
while I was at the comic store.
It’s mind-boggling news,
but it’s absolutely true!
( Koichi wails )
hazamada: Hey,
I just had a great idea.
Let’s get some autographs!
Koichi: You know it!
Just lead the way!
Hazamada: We really
get each other, huh?
Koichi: You think so?
Hey, look up there!
I think that might be
his studio. The light’s on.
Hazamada: Yeah, you’re right.
Koichi: Hey, I wonder
if Rohan has any family.
Hazamada: From what I hear,
he lives alone.
He made his debut
four years ago,
back when he was 16.
Koichi: Say what?!
He’s only 20 years old?
That means he was about my age
when he went pro.
hazamada:
Snooping around out here
won’t do us any good, koichi.
you’re gonna
have to ring the doorbell.
koichi: Huh?
But why do I have to do it?
Hazamada: Isn’t it obvious?
I have seniority over you,
and, to be honest, this kind
of stuff makes me nervous.
( Koichi groans )
That’s not fair at all.
( Hazamada chuckles )
( Koichi sighs )
( Screams )
♪
( Koichi whimpering )
( Screams )
Hazamada: Hey, I recognize him!
It’s Rohan kishibe.
He looks just like his picture
on the cover of that special
new year’s edition.
( Gasps )
I mean Mr. Rohan.
Rohan: And who,
pray tell, are you?
Why are you here,
some kind of prank?
hazamada: No!
We’d never do that! Honest!
we’re students
from budogaoka high school.
koichi: Yeah.
We’re fans of yours, sensei.
Rohan: Fans? Of me?
Really? My address
must have gotten leaked.
Hazamada: That’s not it at all.
I just happened
to hear it in passing.
Hope it’s not too much trouble,
Mr. Rohan,
but could we have
a couple of autographs?
It’d really make our day.
Rohan: So you’re fans, eh?
Tremendous. We might just be
on the same wavelength.
- Hazamada: Uh...
- Rohan: Nothing.
Don’t mind me. Please, come in.
It’d be a pleasure
to sign autographs
for two of my biggest fans.
( Chuckles )
- ( Both gasp )
- Hazamada: You see?
Aren’t you glad we came?
Rohan: I know.
How would you like
a little studio tour
while you’re here?
Both: You’d really let us see
where the magic happens?!
Rohan: I’ve already
finished today’s work,
but if you’re
still interested, then--
both: We are!
Rohan: Come in.
Both: Pardon the intrusion.
- Hazamada: Whoa!
- ( Koichi gasps )
( Rohan chuckles )
( Door creaks )
Here it is.
Hazamada: Ohh! Amazing!
♪
koichi: Whoa!
Those are four-color originals!
( Hazamada yells ) Stunning!
It’s even more powerful
in person!
this is
the most magical day ever!
I’m so glad we’re here!
Koichi: So I have
to know, sensei,
how long have you been
working out of morioh?
Rohan: I’ve been living here
for about three months.
My family lives in s city,
but when I was a child,
we actually
called morioh our home.
Tokyo has its perks,
but it’s too chaotic.
it has none
of morioh’s Serenity
and isn’t at all conducive
to creativity.
and besides, today’s
fax machines and photocopiers
are more advanced
than they’ve ever been.
I can send a complete manuscript
in four hours.
No point living in the city now,
unless you care about status
and all that drivel.
Hazamada: So, uh, what about
your assistants and staff?
How do they factor in?
Rohan: They don’t. I work alone.
- Koichi: What?!
- Hazamada: Huh?!
There’s just no way!
You get 19 pages of complex
drawings done in a week!
- Rohan: Four days, actually.
- Both: What?!
Rohan: Five if they’re in color.
On off days, I amuse myself
with travel and such.
I’m not much of a people person,
which is why I chose
to be a manga artist.
An assistant would only be
an unnecessary hindrance.
Koichi: Wow, that’s so amazing!
Hazamada: You’re a total genius!
Rohan: Please, excuse me.
( Hazamada gasps )
It’s a spider.
( Spider hisses )
Rohan: Suburbia never
ceases to amaze
with its bugs and spiders.
Hazamada: Uh, Mr. Rohan?
Rohan: I see.
Hello, araneus ventricosus.
It inhabits homes and
rural areas across Japan.
It’s an orb-weaving spider,
and a number of them
weave webs day and night. Huh.
By the way, you two, do you know
what it takes to create
captivating stories for manga?
Both: Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
Rohan: Reality.
Reality is the driving force
that makes a drawing
come totally alive.
it’s entertainment
on the highest possible level.
People assume manga is born
of imagination and fantasy,
but they couldn’t be more wrong.
A great manga is one
that captures things
experienced, seen, and felt
by flesh-and-blood beings.
- ( Hazamada gasps )
- Koichi: Huh?
rohan: Take this
exquisite spider, for example,
something a typical city-dweller
would kill in disgust.
The way the legs
connect to the body
and the positions
of its many eyes,
even subtle differences
between the male and female--
a manga artist must understand
each of these elements
to draw a spider.
It’s said a spider’s silk
solidifies when exposed to air,
but have you ever given
any thought to its spinnerets?
- ( Both yelp )
- Rohan: And then there’s
the intricate arrangement
of its internal organs.
How does a spider squirm,
especially when it’s
been sliced open
and awaiting certain death?
To depict reality in detail,
one must know such things.
Koichi: That’s barbaric!
rohan: Silence!
How dare an amateur like you
give Rohan kishibe
his opinion?!
Koichi: No, I wasn’t
voicing my opinion at all!
- i’m sorry.
- ( Hazamada gasps )
Rohan: Now it’s time
for a taste.
( Koichi gasps )
Holy shit.
The stereotype is true.
manga artists
really are total weirdoes.
Rohan: An excellent
expression of agony.
Your vomiting reflex is so raw,
I simply must sketch it!
Hazamada: Really?
( Gags )
rohan: And now
you’re just pretending.
Eh, let’s forget
about the sketch.
It won’t be of any use.
Hazamada: Oh. I’m sorry.
You wanted autographs.
I’ll see if I can find a pen
in the kitchen.
I’ll bring some tea out as well.
Hazamada: You don’t
have to do that.
( Gasps )
Rohan is great. What a process.
Now I know what makes
"pink dark boy" so amazing.
His need to know every single
detail is on another level.
- Koichi: Um, hazamada...
- hazamada: Eh?
Koichi: I know we just got here
and all, but, well, uh,
don’t you think it’s about time
for us to get going?
Hazamada: Say what?
You wanna go home now?
But why? Aren’t you having fun?
Koichi: I can’t really say why
i’m so nervous all of a sudden.
i just have
a bad feeling about this.
My gut has been known to be
wrong on rare occasions,
but right now it’s telling me
that there’s something
really dangerous about Rohan.
Hazamada: Dangerous?
What do you mean by that?
You think he’s a stand user?
koichi: No, no,
it’s nothing like that.
It’s just a weird feeling.
Hazamada: Rohan is what
those hippie artist-types
would call avant-garde,
but that doesn’t mean you should
immediately jump to conclusions
about him being a stand user.
Koichi: I already told you
I don’t think he is one.
I just have a bad feeling,
is all.
Hazamada: Okay, okay,
let’s say Mr. Rohan
actually is a stand user.
That’d be amazing for us,
don’t you think?
How awesome would it be
to have something in common
with a famous manga artist?
But I feel you, so let’s leave.
If something about him’s
giving you the willies,
then let’s go. Come on.
We can always come back.
But one catch!
This thing caught my eye,
so I have to check it out first.
Koichi: A thing? Where?
What are you talking about?
Hazamada: Jeez, koichi,
you’re so dense.
There. It’s on top of the desk,
next to the phone.
Look carefully.
Koichi: Eh?
♪
Ahh! Could that be
what I think it is?!
hazamada:
You better believe it is!
He said he just finished
working on it, remember?
I’ve had my eye on it
since we came in here,
and it’s the real deal!
Koichi: I never dreamed
this would happen!
A freshly drawn manuscript
for "pink dark boy"!
Hang on. Does this mean
no one else has seen it yet?
Hazamada: We’ll go home right
after I get a glimpse of this.
Koichi: We have to get
rohan’s permission first.
Hazamada: You really
don’t know anything
about manga artists,
do you, koichi?
all of these
preprinted manuscripts
are highly confidential
in every sense of the word.
There’s no way he’d let
a couple of outsiders like us
look at a manuscript
before the editor’s even
had a chance to give notes!
It’s common sense!
We’ll take a peek,
then put it right back.
Koichi: This is a horrible idea!
Hazamada: Lighten up! We’re not
hurting anyone by reading it.
( Rohan chuckles )
♪
- ( Hazamada stammers )
- ( Koichi gasps )
( Both gasp )
( Both scream )
Hazamada: What is this feeling?!
aah! I know
it’s a thrilling manga,
but seeing it up close
and personal like this
is giving me major goose bumps
all over my body!
Koichi: Ahh! It’s so good!
hurry up,
and turn the page, hazamada!
I have to know what comes next!
Hazamada: I’m getting emotional!
Rohan: What do you know?
It appears my manuscript’s
compatible with you two
after all. How auspicious.
I had a hunch
you might read it.
Good work, boys. The two of you
are compatible first-time
readers of my new manuscript.
( Hazamada gasps )
Koichi: Ha-hazamada, I...
Hazamada: What’s the matter?
Rohan: You will now experience
my glorious ability,
heaven’s door.
It’s a gateway
to your very souls.
Hazamada: Eh? What do you mean?
Koichi: What is going on?!
Why does my hand feel weird?!
Hazamada: What the--
koichi, what the hell
is happening to you?!
( Koichi screams )
rohan: Many things
are recorded in the human body
over the course of one’s life,
every single thing
from the moment you were born.
To peruse your records, I shall
transform you both into books,
magnificent books that chronicle
your life stories.
Hazamada: No, not me.
Somebody help!
rohan: I believe
you read my manga as well.
( Hazamada gasps )
( Gasps ) It’s happening to me!
rohan: My ability
won’t physically harm you,
so there’s no need to worry.
Koichi: What the hell do you
even want from us, anyway?!
rohan: In manga,
the creator’s sense of reality
is critical, remember?
We went over that.
So now I will read
all about your lives
and experiences thus far,
and these pages
will fill my consciousness
with realistic ideas.
More effective
than an interview.
you will tell me
everything you’ve lived through
with 100% accuracy,
as if I had been there
to experience it myself.
Koichi hirose. Born march 28th,
1984, at 6:27 A.M.
you were delivered
at red cross hospital in s city.
A preemie, at 2,325 grams,
you spent a week
in an Incubator.
a family of four and
an older sister named Ayana.
Yes, I see. In grade school
and middle school
you led
a relatively ordinary life.
You also happen to be
a remarkably genuine soul,
an admirable quality.
- ( Gasps )
- ( Koichi gasps )
Rohan: What is this?
So then, you’re hiding
a secret ability, are you?
Reverb, huh?!
And it seems that there are
other individuals in the world
with these
fantastical abilities!
- You have powers, too?
- ( Hazamada whimpering )
( Rohan groans )
Stand users, huh? Astounding!
Everything in here
dated after April, 1999,
is just extraordinary,
an explosion
of wondrous experiences!
josuke higashikata,
jotaro kujo, yukako yamagishi,
okuyasu nijimura,
tamami kobayashi.
Oh, it’s unbelievable,
incredible,
and utterly captivating.
In these pages, koichi hirose,
i’ve just uncovered
the mother lode
of manga material.
shining diamond,
star platinum, the hand,
love deluxe,
et cetera, et cetera!
( Koichi yelps )
What are you talking about?
What the heck are you
planning to do to us now?!
Rohan: You mean
it isn’t obvious yet?
I’m going to use your memories
to write my manga!
Koichi: Reverb!
( Rohan sighs )
Koichi: I’m only gonna
ask you nicely once
to stop attacking us
with your stand!
If you persist--
( Rohan chuckles )
What will you do?
Strike me with reverb act two’s
sound attack? Just try it.
( Koichi gasps )
Don’t test me.
If you don’t release me
from your stand right now,
I won’t hold back!
This is your last chance!
Rohan: Yes, I know.
There’s actually a section
devoted to that
written on page 11.
you’ve always been
far more timid than most others,
and many tend
to blatantly disrespect you,
but when push comes to shove,
you find the courage
to conquer your fears.
Remarkable. I like you already.
And as for my readers,
they’ll feel the same
once they get to know you.
Koichi: I’m not bluffing,
you hear me?!
I’ll attack if I have to!
Rohan: You really don’t know
when to shut up, do you?
Try it, if you dare!
Koichi: Reverb act two, go!
♪
I don’t get it!
How’d my attack miss?!
Hazamada: You honestly missed
at that range?
I thought you let it
go wide on purpose!
Hate to break it to you,
but your aim is shit.
( Koichi growls )
I won’t miss this time!
Hazamada: Where are
you attacking?!
That wasn’t even close!
rohan:
Unfortunately for you, koichi,
I took the Liberty of placing
a little safety lock on reverb.
You can attack me
to your heart’s content,
but you’re no longer able
to land a blow.
Hazamada: Safety lock?
( Koichi groans )
rohan: Take a look.
It’s in the margin on page 11.
i added that new rule as
a little bit of a safety measure
just in case
you used your stand.
( Koichi whimpering )
Do you see?
This is the awesome power
of heaven’s door.
Through it, I can
use words and pictures
to read people’s experiences
or create brand-new memories.
It doesn’t matter what sort of
tricks you have up your sleeve.
you’ll never
be able to do me harm
as long as I have this power.
Koichi: Shit!
What do I do now?!
( Rohan laughs )
Chin up, koichi,
that’s all the tampering
i intend to do.
if I meddled
with your pages any further,
your precious life
would lose all authenticity,
and you’d no longer be
of any benefit to my work.
All right, now let’s have a look
at your pages, hazamada.
Hazamada: You’re a genius
in every sense of the word, sir!
I respect you so much!
Rohan: I suppose
we’ll see about that.
Now then, you sometimes
find a sense of comfort
in picking on creatures
weaker than you,
like helpless kittens
and small birds.
You want to have
your way with junko,
a junior from class e,
but are too cowardly
to act on it.
Your testicles
often grow sweaty,
and when you adjust them
during class,
nothing thrills you more
than the thought
that someone might see you.
You’re a disgusting troll.
Including someone like you
in my manga
would drive readers away.
- ( Hazamada whimpers )
- Rohan: You’re useless.
( Hazamada wails )
What am I gonna do now?!
I’m hopeless!
- Koichi: Why?
- Rohan: Hmm?
Koichi: Why are you doing this?!
You don’t need any of my
experiences to create stories.
you’re a spectacular
manga artist all on your own!
Every reader in the world
knows that!
Also, you’re only
20 years old
and live in this amazing house!
Think of how blessed you are
compared with most people
your age!
So why do you need my memories
- when you’re already great?!
- ( Rohan growling )
How stupid can you be?!
Do you think that I,
Rohan kishibe,
draw manga to gather money
and admiration?!
I draw manga so that people
around the world will read it.
My only objective is for people
to read my work.
i know it’s
a single, simple reason.
Even so, it’s all I care about.
People want honesty
when they read my work,
so I search for inspirational
realism every day.
And truth be told,
I absolutely love
the feeling
of finishing a manuscript.
Everyone feels good
after finishing a project
they’ve worked hard on,
but that gratification
is fleeting and immaterial.
After the initial rush
of euphoria is gone,
I begin to think no one will
read the manga I slaved over,
and my deep-seated insecurities
begin to flare up.
"What if all my readers
are gone by next week?"
what if I don’t know
what to draw for the next issue?
What if I lose
the ability to draw?
what if
my motivation disappears?"
These are the recurring thoughts
that have tormented me
over and over since I was
a 16-year-old novice,
until three months ago,
when a mysterious stranger
shot me to the core
with an arrow
and I gained
the ability of heaven’s door.
Hazamada: That was
keicho nijimura.
Rohan: Yes, I saw his name
written on your pages.
You two have no idea
what it’s like
to find the perfect inspiration
for your ultimate masterpiece!
But i’ve found it at last!
There’s nothing better!
Koichi, i’m taking your reality
and using it as a muse
for my new stories!
- ( Koichi yelling )
- ( Hazamada groans )
( Rohan laughing )
♪
Hazamada: See, koichi?
I told you Mr. Rohan
was a super nice guy!
aren’t you glad
we decided to pay him a visit?
Koichi: Definitely.
I had a ton of fun.
Not only did he give us
these great autographs,
he was even kind enough
to serve us tea and cookies.
Hazamada: Mm-hmm.
Koichi: I wanna go back
as soon as we can.
Hazamada: Me, too.
Today kicked ass!
Well, i’m headed this way.
See you later.
Koichi: I’m still surprised
he was such a great guy.
♪
Rohan: You’ll never speak
of what happened, right, koichi?
( Koichi yelps )
What the?!
How the heck did I
lose 20 kilograms?
that’s so weird.
I look exactly the same.
Yep. It reads five kilograms,
so the scale’s not broken.
This doesn’t make any sense!
Wait. This must be the work
of an enemy stand user!
There’s no other way
I could possibly lose
20 kilograms this fast,
but who’s the user?
I have to talk
to josuke about thi--
huh?
Ayana: Hey, ko, what are
you doing over there?
Koichi: Huh?
Me? Uh, well, i--
huh. What was it?
Ayana: What the hell are you
talking about, you weirdo?
Girl: Hey, what’s wrong?
Ayana: Oh, it’s just my brother.
For some reason,
he’s wandering around the house
in his goofy boxers.
Koichi: What was it?
I could have sworn
I was thinking about something
really important a second ago.
( Sighs )
Well, if I managed
to forget so easily,
it couldn’t have
been that important.
( Birds chirping )
oh, man.
Why do my shoes and bag
feel heavier than usual today?
Hold on.
♪
Th-this house.
How strange. Somehow I ended up
walking all the way back
to rohan’s house.
The door’s open.
I’d like to drop in
and thank him
for being
such a great host yesterday,
but i’ll be late for school.
I probably shouldn’t.
being an artist,
he’s probably still asleep.
It’d be rude to just barge in.
I really shouldn’t.
( Door creaks )
Josuke: You saw that,
right, okuyasu?
Okuyasu: Yeah.
Josuke: Spying feels wrong,
but it’s out of character
for koichi to act so weird
and ditch school.
What the hell is he doing?
Okuyasu: Well, I wanna know
who in the world lives here.
I mean there’s no way
he’s meetin’ up
with some chick, right?
♪
( Pencil scraping )
( Koichi thinking ) Rohan.
he’s working with
such a chilling expression.
And for some reason,
I can’t shake the feeling
that being in this house
is actually terrifying.
But why?
Rohan: You finally made it.
It’s good to see you.
- Right on time for our session.
- Koichi: Huh?
( Rohan chuckles )
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪