( Birds chirping )
( Tomoko groans ) God damn it.
This frickin' pisses me off.
I don't get it. Where'd the damn thing go?
Jotaro: Anjuro katagiri, a.K.A. Angelo.
Known as the sickest, most heinous criminal
in Japanese history.
He continually murdered from the age of 12,
with his final homicide being...
Tomoko: Hey, milkman! Watch where you step!
Jotaro: ...Fouler than dog shit.
In march of 1994, he came across
three unsuspecting 14-year-old boys,
two of which the monster proceeded to rape and murder.
- Angelo: Ugh. - Tomoko: You step in something?
Angelo: Yeah, I suppose I did.
Tomoko: You know, it frickin' pisses me off,
people letting their dog shit in my yard like that!
And I have half a mind to keep it.
Dumping it in the owner's pocket
tomorrow morning sounds like fair game to me.
Angelo: 'Scuse me. I, uh, left your milk
sitting right over there. Later, then.
♪♪
Tomoko: Just a sec.
I don't think I've seen you around here before.
Angelo: Oh, yeah. I'm just temping for the day.
Tomoko: Hmm.
Jotaro: The third boy
came from an extremely wealthy family,
so Angelo demanded ransom.
That's what led to his arrest.
Tomoko: Well, I hate to nitpick, temp guy,
but the safety seal on this bottle is clearly broken.
Angelo: Huh? That so?
Tomoko: Take a look! It's right here, plain as day.
Angelo: Would you look at that?
Tomoko: I told you it was broken.
Angelo: Yeah. Sorry for the trouble.
So long.
Tomoko: Thanks again for the milk!
Angelo: Don't mention it.
Curse that damn bitch.
That one sure is a sharp-eyed ViXen.
If only that shrew and her punk son josuke
had drunk the milk, my stand, aqua necklace,
would have been in perfect position to conquer those two.
Huh?
- ( Dog farts ) - Owner: I can't believe
you have more in there, you little shitter.
( Angelo gasps )
Jotaro: When the police
finally raided Angelo's torture den,
they found a horrific sight.
The boy had already been murdered,
his genitalia severed
and nailed to a pillar that was standing nearby.
( Dog whimpers )
( Owner gasps )
( Angelo grunting )
( Owner gagging )
Angelo: Worthless bastard.
Don't you know how to pick up after your dog?
And you just had to toss your dirty cig on the ground.
Well, you got what you deserved, shit face!
Wanna be a pompous asshole?
Then you could swallow my stand and die
like the dirty rat you are.
( Aqua necklace laughs )
♪♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Josuke: Well, from where we were watching,
it looked like the stand
forcibly took over the robber's body.
I mean, he jumped in like it was a day at the pool,
but for some reason, he didn't touch a hair on my head.
Jotaro: Was Angelo lurking nearby?
You know, the guy from the picture?
Josuke: If he was, I didn't see him there.
Damn it. I can't do anything with my hair today.
Jotaro: Listen. His stand may not be very strong,
but he can control it from afar,
and its ability to infiltrate bodies
is gonna make things tricky.
Sit tight. I'll be there soon.
- Josuke: Huh? You mean-- - jotaro: Until I get there,
don't eat or drink anything. Do you understand?
Stay away from tap water,
and avoid the bathroom and shower. Got it?
Josuke: Can we slow down a bit?
I haven't exactly told my mom that you're in town yet.
She's as tough as they come,
but the thought of Mr. Joestar can still make her cry.
I think she loves him, even after all this time.
One look at you, and she'll know exactly who you are.
Tomoko: Hey, josuke, where'd you get this picture?
Josuke: Mm?
Tomoko: It's the milkman from this morning.
Do you know him?
- ( Josuke gasps ) - Jotaro: Josuke, what's wrong?!
Josuke: His stand is already inside.
It was hiding in my mom's coffee,
and now it's crawled into her mouth!
Jotaro: Josuke, you there? Hey! Josuke!
Tomoko: So, josuke, do you want some coffee?
Josuke: Mm, that sounds good.
I'll take milk and sugar, if you don't mind.
Tomoko: Milk and sugar, it is.
♪♪
( Gasps )
Hey, josuke, you said milk and sugar, right?
Josuke: Uh, yeah.
I'm back, Mr. Jotaro. Still there?
I managed to catch the little bastard, but...
- Jotaro: What? - ( Aqua necklace groans )
Josuke: I have no idea what to do now.
Jotaro: How in the hell...
Just be careful.
Angelo's probably spying on your house as we speak.
Keep your eyes glued to the stand,
and I'll be there soon.
Angelo was only able to survive his execution
and break out of prison because he had use of a stand.
Still, I don't know the full extent of his abilities.
♪♪
Announcer: Dead ball! Sayonara!
Dead ball! Game over!
- Sayonara! - Josuke: Hmm?
( Aqua necklace roars )
Josuke: Good boy.
Angelo: You bastard.
Tomoko: Josuke...
Angelo: I'm gonna smash your prissy face
and rip your smoking-hot mom to pieces!
I have to find a way to get that cap off,
or maybe I can break the bottle. What am I gonna do?
( Bicycle bell ringing )
( Gasping )
( Ryohei yawns )
Angelo: Wait. Is that...
Ryohei: I'm home.
Angelo: Higashikata.
I knew that name was familiar.
So I've stumbled upon officer higashikata's house.
Last time I saw him, I was just 12.
I know everything there is to know about you, old man,
everything!
- Ryohei: Freeze. - ( Josuke gasps )
Ryohei: Josuke, weren't you supposed to go to class?
Josuke: Gramps! Since when do they
let you take guns home from work?
Ryohei: Since now! Answer the question!
Josuke: Yeah, I'm going! I'm just meeting up
with someone before I leave!
( Ryohei laughs )
You goober! This is only a toy gun, my boy!
( Laughs ) Had you goin', didn't I?
Guess that means the first win of this week goes to me.
Josuke: Yeah, yeah, real funny. You win.
Ryohei: Hmm? What's wrong?
You don't usually take it on the chin like that.
Josuke: I'm fine, and mom left for the day.
Now, shouldn't you be in bed? You must be exhausted
anchor: For our next story,
in a gruesome chain of horrific incidents,
the death count has risen to seven.
In all cases, the victims' eyes and ears were disfigured.
- ( Both grunt ) - Anchor: The incident
seems to be isolated to the town of morioh,
but the police aren't sure whether the trauma is caused
by disease or aggressive behavior.
Ryohei: I've encountered this before.
My gut tells me these occurrences
are undeniably deliberate.
I hope it's not as bad as I think, but make no mistake.
Something wicked's lurking in this town.
Josuke: Grandpa...
( Car horn honks )
He's here.
Announcer: Savor morioh's incomparable mis--
Angelo: I know all of your quirks, higashikata,
including what you drink after work.
If I recall, your drink of choice
is a nice cognac, isn't it?
( Aqua necklace gurgling )
♪♪
Jotaro: Josuke, grab the bottle, and get in the car.
We'll take it where no one'll be able to get hurt.
Josuke: That's a good idea.
( Gasps )
G-grandpa?
Aqua necklace: Josuke higashikata,
you really blew it, kiddo.
You turned your back on the old geezer,
and now he's paid the ultimate price for it.
That's what happens when you get cocky, punk!
( Laughs )
You know, there's nothing quite like the feeling
of bringing a pretentious bastard
crashing down to earth
( together ) In a puddle of despair!
- ( Laughing ) - ( Both grunt )
Shining diamond: Dora-ra-ra-ra-ra-ra!
Aqua necklace: That was impressive.
You almost got me, but almost isn't gonna cut it.
Say goodbye to this world,
'cause you're a dead man walking.
Josuke: I turned away for one second,
and he opened the bottle.
Don't worry, though. I've got this.
I know it doesn't look good, but after my stand heals him,
it'll be like it never happened.
There. All better.
( Gasps )
There's no way that he's--
just wait. He's gonna open his eyes.
My stand has always been able to heal people.
I've done it so many times, I've lost track.
I fixed my friend's bones like it was nothing!
Come on, grandpa! Quit messing around, okay?!
Don't tell me you've already passed out
from last night's shift.
Enough with the jokes! This isn't funny!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Jotaro: Josuke.
Josuke: He's healed, right?
Jotaro: Listen, josuke. It's said the human organism
must destroy in order to survive,
but your power is an unparalleled
act of compassion in a brutal world.
The problem is...
No amount of compassion or love can bring back the dead.
Not even stands have that power.
I'm sorry.
♪♪
Josuke: My grandfather looked after this town for 35 years.
He never once abandoned his post.
He told me that danger was lurking.
As soon as he heard the news report
about Angelo's return to murder,
I looked into his eyes
and saw a man of honor ready to protect.
Jotaro: Angelo's racked up a high body count.
There are probably more victims out there
just waiting to be found.
He kills without motive, murdering for the thrill of it,
and this is only the beginning.
I'm certain that he'll keep killing,
but first he'll kill you and your mother.
( Josuke sighs )
I'll do it.
I'll take the Baton my grandpa left behind
to protect my mom and the town,
and nothing's gonna get in the way of that.
Narrator: Services had come to a close,
and his uniform hung lifelessly in the closet.
Beside it lay all that he once wore.
His shoes, socks, shirt, and pants
recalled a sagacious elder
with the playful spirit of a child.
He was a man who lived life to the fullest.
Eventually even these belongings would be discarded,
for, despite his daughter's reluctance
to part with a single one of her cherished mementos,
his possessions would never be worn by him again.
Koichi: I'd like to be there for him,
but I'm sure he needs his privacy right now.
Jotaro: Don't touch anything that's not from a bottle or can.
We have to be careful.
Where did your mom go?
Josuke: I asked her to go and visit
some of our relatives after the funeral.
Jotaro: That was good thinking.
She can return after we make Angelo pay.
- ( Josuke groans ) - Jotaro: Hmm?
Josuke: Before you say anything, I'm doing fine.
I just got a little worked up hearing his name.
In fact, I've never been calmer in my life.
Jotaro: Yeah, sure.
Ultimately, it's your house,
so I suppose you can take out your anger on whatever you want.
By the way, about that scratch on your lip,
I did that when I punched you, didn't I?
Doesn't your stand possess the ability
to heal your own wounds?
Josuke: That'd be great, wouldn't it?
But, no, it can't.
Jotaro: What if his stand
is somehow able to infiltrate your body
and then tries to eat its way out of you?
Josuke: What do you think?
If he gets me, I'm a dead man.
( Angelo chewing )
I don't know what you're planning,
but my stand's not going back in that bottle.
You've already played your hand,
so I'm one step ahead of the game, my friend.
Your efforts are futile.
I've got all the time in the world,
so hole up in there as long as you want.
I can wait! Hmm.
Jotaro: Bastard's been sniffing around here
right under our noses,
and still he hasn't moved on us in three days.
But why? What the hell's he waiting for?
♪♪
( Sighs ) It's raining.
( Gasps ) Raining.
- Wait. - ( Angelo chuckles )
Star platinum: Ora!
Aqua necklace: Interesting.
I knew you were a weird one,
but I didn't think you'd be a stand user.
( Scoffs ) No matter.
My moment has finally arrived,
'cause this house belongs to me now,
and thanks to this rain, you're not going anywhere.
Jotaro: Josuke!
Josuke: By the looks of things,
he must have gotten all this water boiling.
He even turned on the hot water faucets, too.
Jotaro: To make matters worse, his stand is in the house.
Turns out he hasn't been waiting for us to drink the water.
He's been waiting for the rain.
His stand can move anywhere in the rain.
No. It can change between liquid and vapor.
Josuke! Hurry, and get away from the kettle!
He morphed into steam!
( Shining diamond yelling )
Josuke: Things just got a lot more difficult.
We can't catch him with the bottle anymore.
Jotaro: For now, stay away from any steam,
and protect your lungs.
The priority is getting out of here.
Joseph: Easier said than done.
I'm not sure we have much of a choice
as far as leaving's concerned.
Of course. Angelo's already put
a bunch of holes in the roof to make his job easier.
Upstairs is no good,
and we'll be sitting ducks if we go outside.
Aw, this is just great.
( Jotaro gasps )
( Josuke gasps )
( Aqua necklace growls )
Jotaro: I have to be honest with you.
This liquid morphing stand is way more than I bargained for.
Plus, it's really freaky.
He's a clever bastard.
( Josuke laughing )
Jotaro: What's so funny?
The son of a bitch has cornered us.
- ( Josuke laughing ) - Jotaro: Hey!
Josuke: It's fine, Mr. Jotaro.
My grandpa's murderer has been kind enough to turn himself in.
It's pretty great, don't you think?
( Angelo laughs )
Okay, it's time to finish them once and for all.
( Aqua necklace laughs )
Star platinum: Ora!
Ora!
( Aqua necklace jabbers )
Star platinum: Ora!
( Aqua necklace laughs )
Jotaro: I'm all ears, josuke.
If you have a plan, now's the time.
How do we get out of this?
Josuke: "Get out," huh?
Getting out isn't exactly what I had in mind.
( Yells )
Shining diamond: Dora!
Josuke: Breaking out works better.
Come on. This way.
The wall's gonna repair itself.
Jotaro: Good grief.
Josuke: Well, we blocked the steam, at least.
( Both gasp )
Jotaro: The humidifier!
- ( Josuke gasps ) - Jotaro: Josuke!
Aqua necklace: I'm the winner.
I predicted that you'd break through the wall
and flee into this room, seeking shelter!
Jotaro: Shit. Too late.
( Angelo chuckles )
I guess it's like picking all the right answers.
Or maybe I should compare it to winning at the races.
Either way, you can't help but let out a little giggle
when you end up being the Victor!
That euphoria's one of the best feelings in the world!
- ( Laughs ) - ( Josuke gagging )
Jotaro: Josuke!
Josuke: Angelo thinks he's won,
but he's got it wrong, Mr. Jotaro.
Jotaro: Josuke.
Josuke: When this battle goes the way I know it will,
I can promise you I won't feel like laughing in the least,
not when I'm fighting a horrible person like Angelo.
( Yells )
( Aqua necklace yells )
Jotaro: Is that...
Josuke: You bet it is.
It's kinda gross, though. Sorry about that.
I cut a rubber glove into little pieces
and swallowed it earlier.
♪♪
( Shining diamond yells )
( Angelo yells )
Jotaro: Good thinking. Now we know where Angelo is.
( Angelo groans )
( Panting )
Shit. Shit.
( Groans )
( Gasps )
Well, what do you know?
Jotaro: It's Angelo.
Angelo: Screw the both of you!
( Groans )
Easy now. I don't know what you're thinking,
but you can't be serious about killing me.
Okay, I admit it. I escaped that hellhole called death row.
And, sure, I may have been found guilty under Japanese law,
but you guys have no right to do anything to me!
Josuke, let's be frank. Yeah, I murdered your grandpa,
but that doesn't mean you can put me to death, too!
If you kill me, you'll end up cursed,
just like yours truly,
so back off if you know what's good for you! ( Laughs )
- Shining diamond: Dora! - ( Angelo screams )
Josuke: It's rude to point your finger at people.
Didn't your mother ever teach you that?
( Angelo gasps )
What the hell did you do to my hand?!
Josuke: You should take solace
in the fact no one's gonna execute you,
not me and not this guy either.
We won't be killing you,
nor will we be turning you in to the police.
Jotaro: Josuke, you handle the rest.
Angelo: What the hell
are you psychotic bastards planning to do?!
Josuke: Enjoy your eternal penance, Angelo!
Reflect on the life you stole
from my grandpa and all the others!
( Shining diamond yelling )
( Angelo groaning )
Josuke: Here you'll remain for all eternity
in the town my grandpa loved.
( Angelo groaning )
Narrator: Angelo's rock, a popular town landmark
that's well known for being a hot spot
for romantic rendezvous.
For years, it's charmed the residents of morioh,
despite its disturbing appearance.
( Angelo groaning )
( Jotaro thinking ) Jeez. This kid is bat-shit crazy.
( Thinking ) Good grief.
♪♪
♪ Anytime I need to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes, and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don't need to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight, and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in, and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you'll never know what hit you when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don't know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, I'd die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don't know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, I'd die to find out ♪