singers:
♪ mori, mori, mori, mori
♪ morioh Cho radio
- ♪ morioh Cho radio
- Kai: Rise and shine.
Welcome to morioh radio.
as usual,
this is your host, Kai harada,
keeping you company
on this fine morning,
and i’ve got just the song
to start you off right.
- ( Rock ballad playing )
- ( Snipping )
( Snipping continues )
- ♪ Babe, I will
take you anywhere... ♪
Kira: Now let’s dig in,
shall we?
Oh, but before we begin, I have
a little something for you.
♪ And i’m here
to make you smile ♪
♪ and i’m here hanging down
♪ babe, all your lies,
I will survive ♪
- ( Music crackling )
- ♪ babe...
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Woman: Excuse me. Mr. Kira?
♪
Kira: Hmm?
Woman: Mr. Kira, I know
this is super last-minute,
but would you be interested
in getting lunch with us?
Kira: Apologies,
but I must decline.
i need to finish
delivering these documents
before the day
gets away from me.
Enjoy your lunch.
Man: Don’t waste
your time on him.
Woman: Hmm?
Man: He’d suck the life
out of the party.
the guys and I
invite him out on occasion,
but we can never tell
if he’s having fun or hates us.
Yoshikage Kira, age 33, single.
He’s a model employee,
that’s for damn sure,
but the guy’s
dull as dishwater.
it’s not that he’s
necessarily a tool or anything.
He’s just kind of blah,
you know?
♪
Kira: Oh, is that right?
Someone’s a little
bent out of shape.
Some new girls at work
invited me to lunch.
really,
it’s as innocent as that.
but I promised you
lunch was our time together.
I’d never go back on my word
just to fraternize with them.
You heard me turn them down,
didn’t you?
in the time
we’ve known each other,
i’ve never left you
by your lonesome, right?
Good. It’s settled.
Now stop this silly fretting,
and let’s pick out
some sandwiches.
Now, which one do you want?
mmm, this one
has a delicate texture.
This bakery’s
one of my favorites.
It makes sandwiches with bread
made fresh at 11 A.M.
They’re all the rage
around here.
You’d be lucky to find one
on the shelf after 1 P.M.
Even through the wrapper,
you can feel
they’re fresh from the oven.
The katsu they use
is always freshly fried
and perfectly crispy.
What have we here?
It seems in all the excitement,
you managed to tear the wrapper
and make a mess.
Hmm. Such a naughty girl.
♪
( Shudders )
Ah...
( Sighing, slurping )
it’s a waste,
but this sandwich is ruined now.
i suppose we’ll
just buy the one underneath.
Clerk: Thank you
for dropping by.
♪
( Birds chirping )
( Kira chewing )
Simply beautiful, isn’t it?
Quaint, little morioh.
Between us, it might be the most
marvelous town on earth.
It’s like we’re
on a romantic picnic.
( Gasps )
( Sniffing )
( Grumbling )
( Sniffs )
A bit aromatic for my taste.
i think it’s time
for the two of us to part ways.
The end is close at hand.
"Close at hand." ( Chuckles )
If luck is on my side,
perhaps i’ll cross paths
with a beautiful new girl
visiting from out of town.
- ( Brush rustles )
- huh?
♪
( Dog panting )
Kira: Oh, joy. It’s a mutt.
♪
( Dog whimpers )
( Chewing )
- Josuke: Huh?
- Okuyasu: Shigechi!
Shigechi: Eh?
Hey!
Josuke and okuyasu,
good to see you.
Okuyasu: What’s up? You know,
you got here
just in the Nick of time.
josuke: I’ll get
right to the point, okay?
We need to borrow
some lunch money.
We’re a little strapped for cash
at the moment.
shigechi: Huh?
How’s that even possible?
What happened to the money
we got from the lottery ticket?
Is it gone already?
Okuyasu: Don’t be silly!
We put all that in the bank,
and you gotta be crazy
if you think we’d go
all the way to the bank
just to get some lunch money.
It’s not worth the walk.
A thousand yen should be
enough for both of us.
Josuke: I agree.
okuyasu: Come on.
As soon as school’s over,
we’ll head to the bank
and pay you back.
Josuke: Hey, I know that logo.
you got a sandwich
from St. gentlemen, didn’t you?
- okuyasu: Whoa!
- Josuke: Well, whaddaya know.
- I thought they were sold out.
- Shigechi: They are,
and you’re not getting a single
bite of mine! You got that?
Eh, if you leave
my sandwich alone,
i’ll lend you guys the money.
Josuke: Sweet!
Okuyasu: I can taste
our lunch already.
Josuke: Thank you.
Shigechi: And just so you know,
i’m writing an I.O.U.
For this little loan.
You’re not gonna
weasel out of this one.
okuyasu: Me? You’re
the biggest weasel there is!
Shigechi: Okay. "June 24th..."
Josuke: Thanks a lot, shigechi.
Shigechi: "Lent 1,000 yen
to needy friends."
Hang on. "Lent."
How do you write the character
for "lent" again?
Oh, well. This’ll work for now.
I guess hiragana’s
better than nothing.
Crud monkeys. I don’t know
how to write "josuke"
or "okuyasu" either.
Eh? What the?!
My sandwich was right there!
Where did it go?
( Gasping )
♪
( Sighs )
what a relief.
My sandwich is safe and sound.
I don’t remember it
being this far away,
but at least I found it.
Kira: Huh?
Hmm?
( Gasps )
♪
( Shigechi panting )
Kira: Th-that’s...
Shigechi: Hey, josuke,
okuyasu, wait up!
We’re not done yet!
I need your thumbprints on
my I.O.U. To make it official!
Kira: Huh?
( Dog grunting )
Kira: You have
got to be kidding me.
That lump of a brat
grabbed my bag by mistake.
josuke: Come on.
Could you be any more annoying?
How would we give you
our thumbprints?
Okuyasu: It’s simple.
You cut your thumb with a knife
and use the blood.
Shigechi: What are
you talking about?!
We don’t have to go that far.
Just sign the I.O.U.,
and we’ll call it good.
Okuyasu: Yeah, yeah, but let’s
haul ass to St. gentlemen
before they sell out.
Kira: Damn it.
I can’t let him see
what’s in that bag.
She’s still wearing the ring I
put on her finger this morning.
It has my fingerprints on it,
so when the police
open an investigation,
it’ll be just a matter of time
before they trace it back to me.
yoshikage Kira
has been at this for 15 years,
and in all that time,
he’s never left a single clue.
This pathetic whelp
isn’t changing that.
Okuyasu: Hey, josuke,
let’s head in.
Josuke: Right.
Shigechi: I’ll stay outside
and wait for you guys.
Kira: My best bet
is to take it by force.
On second thought, i’d better
snatch it without his knowing.
♪
Okuyasu: Shigechi!
You’re a lucky son of a gun.
You know that?
Josuke: The lunchtime rush
beat us here,
and they’re already out
of St. gentlemen sandwiches.
Just our luck.
Shigechi: They’re sold out, huh?
( Mocking )
Well, isn’t that a shame?
I feel bad for you guys.
i really do.
I guess I could sell you mine,
but, so you know,
it’ll cost you 10,000 yen. ’kay?
- ( Laughs )
- ( Kira growling )
Okuyasu: Boy, not a decent bone
in your body, is there?
All right, josuke, looks like
we’re heading to hokaben.
Josuke: You sure
that’ll be enough?
I doubt a 500-yen meal
and a drink will fill us up.
We’re better off skipping it.
It’s not my first choice,
but the cafeteria
will do just fine.
Besides, that’s where koichi
said he’s getting lunch today.
Okuyasu: Aw, man,
that means he’ll be there
with yukako yamagishi.
I hate having to be
the third wheel
to those honeymooners’s
lovefest.
And the food they serve
is terrible.
Their nasty meat is so thin,
it’s practically invisible.
And who knows what kinda weird
shit they put in the miso soup?
Shigechi: Hey! Why don’t we
use the equipment room
at my middle school’s gym?
It has tons of drinks
to choose from.
Our p.E. Teacher
always sneaks away
to have his coffee and tea
in there when no one’s looking.
All the teachers are in
the faculty room during lunch,
so they won’t
be able to bust us.
Sometimes i’ll sneak in
through the window
and take a cup
to quench my thirst.
Why don’t you go buy lunch,
and we’ll hang out there
and eat together.
Josuke: Let’s back it up there,
shigechi.
are you seriously
stealing drinks from school?
Okuyasu: You stingy bastard!
can’t you even
buy drinks for yourself?
you’d never see me
doing something that greedy.
See you later.
shigechi: Jeez,
what crawled up their butts?
I was just trying to be nice.
Okay, well...
You better pay me back
my thousand yen tomorrow!
♪
Hmph.
- ( Kira gasps )
- ( Shigechi gasps )
Sorry for bumping
into you, sir.
It’s all my fault. I wasn’t
looking where I was going.
Sorry again.
Kira: Shit, so close.
He’s left his idiotic friends,
but he’s heading back to school.
He’s eating lunch there,
so what’s my next move?
i believe
they call him shigechi.
Minutes from now,
he’ll open that bag,
and things will get
very complicated.
Damn it. This is unfathomable.
( Shigechi chuckling )
all righty, now that
i’m in my special hidey spot,
i can finally
eat my lunch in peace.
♪
( Kira gasps )
Shigechi: Oh, yeah.
How did I almost forget?
before I start
chowing down on my food,
I need to make coffee.
It’s not a secret trip
to the gym
without a freshly brewed cup.
( Chuckling )
Kira: Fortune has smiled
on you, shigechi.
Had you peaked inside,
my only recourse would have
been to obliterate you.
♪
okuyasu: Josuke,
I think this is the place.
- ( Kira gasps )
- ( Okuyasu grunts )
It’s smaller than I thought.
Kira: What the?
Why are they here?
I thought these two
were blowing him off.
Okuyasu: Shigechi,
you here or what?
Shigechi!
Shigechi: Huh? Hey,
what are you doing here?
i thought you were
gonna get lunch somewhere else.
Josuke: That was the plan,
but we couldn’t just pass up
free coffee from café gym.
Okuyasu: We got 500-yen
makunouchi bentos on the way.
( Laughs )
Shigechi: Wow, I can’t believe
you two actually
showed up to eat
after calling me
a stingy bastard.
you’re a couple
of hypocritical pricks.
Josuke: Come on, man.
Cut us some slack.
haven’t you heard
of people changing their minds?
it is a thing
that happens, you know?
( Kira groans )
Now what do I do?
offing one of them
would be a walk in the park,
but I can’t tackle
all three at once.
Shit. I was so close, too.
She’s only centimeters away.
- ( Clatter )
- Kira: Huh?
josuke: Shigechi,
you mind grabbing me a drink
on your way back?
and could you make it
a green tea instead of coffee?
Okuyasu: I’ll take
a black tea with milk.
shigechi: Really?
Makunouchi with milk tea?
That sounds disgusting.
Kira: Shit! He’s going
to try to eat his meal
right on top of this thing.
If I don’t do something fast,
he’s going to open the bag
right in front of them. Huh?
okuyasu: Aw,
not soy sauce again.
They’re always givin’ me
soy sauce with katsu.
Josuke: Huh? That’s how
you’re supposed to eat it.
Okuyasu: No way!
Don’t be stupid.
Everyone knows
it’s tonkatsu sauce.
Putting soy sauce on tonkatsu
violates all that’s sacred.
Josuke: Like it matters.
♪
Kira: Yes.
( Gasps )
- Josuke: Hmm?
- Okuyasu: Eh?
Kira: Damn it.
Josuke: What the hell?
♪
- Okuyasu: Eh?
Kira: Damn it.
Josuke: What the hell?
♪
Shigechi: Just a minute!
What exactly do you
think you’re doing?
Talk! ’cause from where
i’m standing, it looks like
you’re trying to steal
my sandwich out from under me.
josuke: As if!
Stop being such an idiot.
I came over here, ’cause I
thought I heard something weird.
I was gonna check it out
and then get back to eating.
Shigechi: My food’s
off limits, hear me?!
I can already hear
your sappy sob story.
"Teriyaki chicken sandwiches
are my favorite,
so won’t you please give me
a teeny-weeny bite, shigechi?"
Tell me i’m wrong!
- You can’t, can you?
- ( Josuke groans )
You sure are a greedy
little stinker, aren’t you?
Why don’t you focus
on bringing out my tea?
Okuyasu: Oh, and don’t
forget my milk tea!
Shigechi: I’m making ’em
fast as I can.
( Grumbles )
Kira: Now.
♪
Josuke: Eh?
Kira: I did it.
shigechi: ’kay,
get ’em while they’re hot,
one green tea and
one black tea with milk.
- ( Okuyasu sighs )
- Josuke: Thanks.
( Shigechi gasps )
Josuke: Eh?
Okuyasu: What’s with you?
shigechi:
My sandwich disappeared!
What did you lunch thieves
do with it?!
okuyasu:
Lunch thieves? Who, us?
Josuke: It’s definitely gone,
but we didn’t have
anything to do with it.
- Tell him, okuyasu.
- Okuyasu: What he said.
Shigechi: I’ve had
enough of your games!
There’s no one else here but us!
you gotta know
what happened to my sandwich!
Josuke: We don’t! Seriously,
we’re telling you the truth.
Okuyasu: Yeah, cross our hearts.
We’re not messin’ around.
We’re just as confused
about all this as you are.
Shigechi: You lying punks.
Fine. Now you’ve gone
and made me angry.
Josuke: It’s the truth.
Okuyasu: I’ve had enough of you
pointing the finger at us.
Why would we take your sandwich
when we’ve got--
shigechi: If you’re gonna lie,
then we’ll do things my way!
All I have to do is make harvest
turn this room inside out.
Okuyasu: Damn,
you are so annoying.
Fine. Search the room.
i want you to.
Search until you pass out.
Go for it.
Josuke: For the last time,
why would we steal
a stupid sandwich?
♪
Kira: This is torture.
What’s going on out there?
I can’t see a thing
trapped under here.
I don’t know what
that pissant is up to,
but it can’t be anything good.
- Man: Hey, open up!
- ( Lock clicking )
I know somebody’s in here!
Shigechi: Shit balls!
we’re busted!
- It’s the p.E. Teacher!
- josuke: Crap!
Then it’s time to bail!
let’s go!
Shigechi: I can’t leave! I still
haven’t found my sandwich!
Josuke: Now’s not the time!
Out you go!
Teacher: Get back here!
( Boys panting )
Okuyasu: Let’s beat it!
( Teacher scoffs )
No-good hooligans.
I thought my tea and coffee
wasn’t lasting very long.
I thought I was going crazy,
but I was just being used.
I have to start
locking this place up
tighter than fort Knox.
( Footsteps )
( Door closes )
♪
Kira: This day
has been hellacious,
but despite every setback,
I beat the odds
and have been reunited
with my girl.
i can’t explain it,
but i’ve always had the feeling
that somewhere out there
is a guardian angel
looking over
yoshikage kira’s shoulder,
that, in the end, things
will work out for the best
and, if I live every day
with rigor and boldness,
i’ll ultimately be delivered
from a wretched life.
( Chuckles )
We had a pretty close call
today, my dear,
but I knew we’d find
our way back to each other.
♪
- Shigechi: I found it.
- Kira: Hmm?
Shigechi: Now why is someone
i’ve never laid eyes on
skulking off with my sandwich?
and while we’re
on the subject, buster,
why is some strange man
hanging around my school
like it’s another day
at the office?
Kira: Pardon? You wouldn’t
happen to be talking to me,
would you, little boy?
Because I haven’t
the faintest idea
what you’re going on about.
If you must know,
I just purchased this item
at St. gentlemen.
Shigechi: You can save
the bullshit.
That bag’s my property.
I could go on and on
about how I know it’s mine,
but someone like you
would never understand.
Time to take back
what’s ours, harvest!
( Kira gasps ) Blast it!
What the hell is happening?
The bag’s being ripped away!
( Gasps )
( Shigechi gasps )
Wait. What?! No way!
I don’t understand
what’s going on!
That’s not my sandwich!
Oh, god.
Did that hand come
from a real person?
Kira: So it’s come to this, eh?
My secret is out.
Interestingly enough, you and I,
it would appear that we both
share a unique power, but how?
Shigechi: What’d you just say?
Can you see my harvest?
No, that’s not important
right now.
Why are you strutting around,
carrying a hand in your bag?
That’s so freaky!
Kira: You’re by yourself,
i presume?
i don’t see
your playmates anywhere.
I believe their names
were josuke and okuyasu?
Would it be safe to assume
they both have powers
similar to ours?
shigechi: Oh, no!
Don’t you move a single muscle!
If you so much as blink,
you’re a goner!
My gut’s sayin’ you’re
some kind of closet weirdo,
and I don’t want you
coming any closer,
so stay there if you know
what’s good for you!
Just looking at your slimy face
is starting
to make my skin crawl.
You’re evil, and evil people
need to stay far away. Ahh!
Kira: You can call me
yoshikage Kira.
I’m currently 33 years old.
Not that you’d care,
but I reside in northeast
morioh’s villa district.
Also, i’ve yet to marry.
( Shigechi gasping )
Kira: In order to make a living,
I work for kameyu
department stores.
After a long day’s work,
I return home
no later than 8 P.M.
( Shigechi gasps )
Kira: I don’t like smoking,
but do enjoy
the occasional drink.
I’m always in bed by 11 P.M.,
and I make it a point
to get no less than eight hours
of sleep each night.
Shigechi: Uh...
kira: Before bed,
I drink a warm glass of milk.
it’s always coupled
with 20 minutes of stretching
to decompress
from the long workday.
sweet dreams are
the usual result of this.
Shigechi: Eh...
Kira: I then awake as refreshed
and recharged
as a newborn child,
ready to take on
the day’s challenges.
And after my last checkup, I was
given a clean bill of health.
shigechi: Hey,
what’s the big idea, creeper?
Why are telling me this crap?
Kira: For as long
as I can remember,
i’ve done everything in my power
to live a productive life
that allows me to pursue
a lasting, inner peace.
This may be a foreign concept,
but I choose not to concern
myself with winning or losing,
life’s troubles, or enemies
who bring sleepless nights.
That is how I cope
with this backwards life
we find ourselves living.
It’s what brings me happiness
in a world fraught
with hardship and misery.
Of course, if I were
ever to engage in combat,
I would win the battle
without question.
( Shigechi gasping )
Kira: In other words, shigechi,
you are an irksome troublemaker
who stands to hinder my sleep.
You, boy, are the enemy.
( Shigechi gasps ) That’s...
Kira: Deadly queen.
I named it myself,
and truth be told,
i’m quite proud of the moniker.
But before you have the chance
to utter a word of this
to another soul,
I shall eradicate you.
I’ll sleep soundly tonight.
I can already feel it.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪