♪
kai: Good morning,
and welcome to morioh radio.
today we have a letter
from languishing lonesome boy.
"Kai, hear me out," he writes.
"My girlfriend just ghosted me,
and i’m super depressed.
I think I may
have scared her off
with my
out-of-the-blue proposal.
And I spent my whole paycheck
on her birthstone
engagement ring, too."
♪
( All gasp )
Josuke: So you managed to get
the bow and arrow back, huh?
Jotaro: Yeah. I found it
in akira’s apartment.
He’d been using his stand
to help himself
to whatever he wanted.
It all totaled up
to be 500 million yen,
and the police
are already on it.
You can try using your stand
if you want,
but then i’d be forced to hunt
you down and finish you off.
( Akira whimpers )
You can’t lay a finger on me
while i’m in here.
Jotaro: Chili pepper
has been retired.
Even if he broke out,
I doubt he’d attack us.
( Okuyasu sighs )
koichi: Mr. Jotaro,
what about the bow and arrow?
jotaro: It’s going
to the speedwagon foundation
for analysis.
If things go the way I want,
we’ll unlock
the mystery of stands.
Josuke: Great.
Koichi: That’s fantastic.
After you’re done,
all of this will be over.
It feels weird celebrating,
but whoo-hoo!
We cracked the case!
Josuke: We’re still
questioning otoishi
about the other stand users.
There’s no way of knowing
how many he awakened.
you’ll need
to stay on your toes.
- Okuyasu: Got it.
- Koichi: Right.
Joseph: The Japanese sure
know how to make a cup of Joe.
Waitress! Refill, please.
( Josuke gasps ) Careful!
Pay attention.
I swear, you’re such a klutz.
I can’t turn around
for one second.
- ( Josuke sighs )
- ( Koichi chuckles )
Uh, josuke, it’s almost time
for the bus, isn’t it?
Josuke: Eh?
Oh, uh, yeah.
I guess you’re right.
Come on. Get up. We gotta go.
Joseph: Uh...
( Fork clinking )
Koichi: You think those two
are gonna be okay?
I’m kinda worried.
- jotaro: Hmm.
- Okuyasu: Holy cannoli!
This is the yummiest cake
i’ve ever tasted!
waitress,
I want some more, please!
- ( Vacuum whirring )
- ( Telephone ringing )
- Tomoko: Huh?
- ( Vacuum stops )
This is tomoko.
- May I ask who’s speaking?
- Josuke: Oh, hey, mom.
- It’s me.
- Tomoko: Hmm?
Josuke? This is a surprise.
You never call the house.
Are you in some kind of trouble?
josuke: No.
Uh, why would you think that?
Uh, anyway, you’re gonna be home
for the rest of the day, right?
Tomoko: Yeah, that’s the plan.
Is there something
I should know?
Josuke: No, I just wanted
to make sure. Bye.
- ( Hangs up )
- Tomoko: Hey, wait!
What in the world? I swear,
that kid had better
not be up to anything fishy.
Josuke: That was a close one.
I hope mom doesn’t think
something’s up.
this’ll be hard enough
without her catching on early.
Eh?
You’ve gotta be kidding!
I told that old geezer to wait
until I was off the phone.
♪
Mm. ( Groans )
Hey, wait up.
Did you hear me?!
I asked you to slow down,
old man!
Joseph: Sorry about that.
You weren’t calling after me,
were you?
Josuke: Forget it. We’ll never
flag down a cab at this hour,
so we’re gonna have
to take a bus to my house.
Oh, one more thing.
I know this sounds kinda pushy,
but it has to be said now.
Joseph: Eh?
Josuke: Make sure you
keep your distance from mom,
and no talking to her.
Before we go anywhere,
you have to promise me.
The terms are non-negotiable.
Because if I know my mother,
a simple visit
won’t be enough for her.
she’ll become
an emotional train wreck.
Joseph: Hmm.
I’m well aware.
All right, then. I promise.
Josuke: And so we’re clear,
i’m not-- i’m gonna be
calling you Mr. Joestar
the entire time you’re here.
Joseph: Eh?
Josuke: Look, this is awkward,
but I need to be
as clear as possible.
Strangers, that’s all
the two of us were ’til now.
I know that sounds kinda harsh,
but it’s the truth.
Like it or not,
calling you my father
just isn’t something
i’m willing to do.
( Joseph sighs )
Josuke: Here’s the deal.
After you see mom, you should
hurry back to America.
Joseph: Hmm?
Yes, you’re right.
I completely understand.
Sorry to trouble you.
Josuke: Shit.
i don’t think this
could be any more awkward.
I know the best thing
would be to open up,
but you can’t force
what isn’t meant to be.
( Sighs )
Hey, Mr. Joesta-- eh?
( Gasps )
’scuse me. By any chance,
did a big,
grandpa-looking guy walk by?
Woman: He just got
on that long-haul bus.
Josuke: Huh?
What the hell
were you thinking?!
( Panting )
Joseph: Sorry for the hassle.
You said we were going
to get on a bus, so I did,
and it would seem you caught up
not a minute too soon.
From the looks of things,
we were just about to merge
onto the freeway.
Josuke: I’m starting to think
I should have let that damn bus
take you
all the way to hokkaido!
At least then i’d--( Groans )
Damn stomach cramp.
Joseph: I didn’t mean
to inconvenience you.
( Gasps )
Hey, josuke,
it sorta feels like something’s
pulling at my pants leg.
Josuke: Yeah? Better be careful.
If you drop your guard,
it’ll drag you off somewhere
and eat you.
( Joseph gasping )
♪
Eh?
J-josuke! Get over here!
- We’ve got a stand user!
- ( Josuke groans )
Oh, yeah, you’re right.
In fact, there are two users.
And for the record,
i’m talking about us.
I’m really thirsty.
( Joseph gasps )
W-wait a minute.
These aren’t footprints.
Hands? They’re handprints.
( Child giggles )
Joseph: Oh, my god!
The stand just laughed, josuke!
Did you hear that?!
It’s right there!
You can see it in the sand!
josuke: Yeah,
there’s no way in hell
i’m letting him meet mom now,
not when he’s seeing
and hearing things.
Joseph: If it weren’t for
all this dag-blasted concrete,
i could find it.
Where’d it go? It vanished!
Why did you disappear?!
Come back!
( Josuke gasps ) Great.
this old man
is nothing but trouble.
( Dog growling )
Joseph: Eh?
- ( Gasps )
- ( Dog snarls )
Joseph: Hermit purple!
( Josuke gasps )
Joseph: Ohh!
- ( Child crying )
- Josuke: Huh?!
( Dog barking )
Joseph: Beat it, mutt.
Go on. Shoo, shoo! Get!
Josuke: Hey, uh, am I crazy,
or is that crying?
- ( Crying continues )
- Joseph: Over here, josuke.
Josuke: Hmm?
Joseph: It’s just a baby.
I’m holding a tiny,
naked baby in my hands.
I know it sounds strange,
but it’s invisible.
Josuke: What?!
( Crying continues )
( Josuke stammering )
It’s hard to believe,
but you’re right.
I can feel its soft skin.
How’s this even possible?
A bona fide invisible baby!
Joseph: From what I can tell,
it can’t be any older
than six months.
Josuke: I wanna know
how it turned invisible
in the first place,
and how’d it get out here?
i’m guessing
it’s the work of a stand,
but why on earth
would an enemy stand user
turn a baby invisible?
And where the hell
is this kid’s mother?
Nothing about this
makes any sense.
Joseph: Huh.
Hey, josuke, call me crazy,
but I think the baby
is the stand user.
- Josuke: What?
- Joseph: Yeah,
it just isn’t aware
of its abilities yet.
Whenever it was separated
from its mother,
the poor little thing
must have turned invisible
- based on pure instinct.
- josuke: Huh?
Joseph: Duress in adults
can trigger ulcers,
hair loss,
and premature graying,
but in the case of this baby,
it’s activated its stand powers.
If we can find its mother,
I think we might be able
to solve this.
( Baby crying )
Josuke: Aw, freakin’ great.
Well, don’t just stand there.
Make it stop crying.
Joseph: I, uh, don’t exactly
know how to do that.
I have a little bit
of experience with this,
but that was a long time ago.
There, there.
Coochie-coochie coo.
Ahh! So that’s where it is.
Josuke: Eh?! Well,
is it a boy or a girl?
Joseph: Yep, this hand
has never let me down.
( Josuke gasps )
Joseph: Hmm.
I’m pleased to say
it’s a girl.
Josuke: Oh, I get it.
That’s why you had
to use your hand, right?
How else could you tell?
( Both yelling )
( Joseph yelps )
Josuke: There something else
I should know about?
Joseph: Josuke...
Do you have any tissues?
Josuke: Eh? ( Sniffs )
Ugh!
Th-that nauseating smell,
why the hell
is it coming from your hand?
Are you saying she--
Joseph: Yeah. I had no idea
she’d even done it
until I got
a noseful of nasty,
and I just finished scratching
my beard with this hand.
( Baby babbles )
man: Here.
I’m returning your manuscript.
I’m looking forward
to the revisions
on the second draft.
Do your best.
Josuke: We’re stuck
with her for now,
so it looks like we’ll need
to pick up formula and diapers,
and since we don’t want her
going au naturel,
she needs some clothes.
♪
I’m counting on you,
mr. Joestar.
Joseph: What? You want me
to buy everything?
Josuke: Yeah.
I can’t go in there.
you have any idea
how that would look to people?
somebody could walk by
and catch me buying baby stuff.
People would start to talk.
They’d see me as some
stupid 16-year-old bad boy
who knocked up some poor chick.
Joseph: Okay, I see your point,
but I only have American
traveler’s checks at the moment.
( Josuke groans )
I guess I have no choice.
Put whatever you buy
on my card.
Joseph: Sorry.
josuke: Stay away
from all the expensive stuff!
I’ve worked my ass off
to build up
that little nest egg. Got it?
joseph:
Yeah, yeah, I understand.
shopkeeper:
Welcome, my good sir.
is there something
I can assist you with today?
Joseph: Possibly. Do you have
disposable diapers here?
shopkeeper:
You bet your bonnet we do.
Is this your first time?
Joseph: Hmm? Well, yeah,
i suppose it is.
Shopkeeper: These diapers
are a cinch to change,
even for customers able to live
at home without assistance.
You’ll rest well with these.
( Joseph stammers )
No. Uh, the diapers
aren’t for me.
They’re for a baby
i’m looking after.
Shopkeeper: Goodness!
I’m sorry. How rude of me.
Of course they’re for a baby.
- ( Laughs )
- ( Joseph sighs )
Shopkeeper: First off, would you
like traditional diapers
or maybe training pants?
Joseph: Hmm? Beg your pardon?
Shopkeeper: As you can see,
although traditional diapers
require a cover,
they’re far more economical
and less wasteful
than training pants.
joseph:
Well, i’m not really sure.
Can I just have this one
right here?
shopkeeper:
And what size would you like?
Joseph: What do you mean?
shopkeeper:
How old is the baby, sir?
Depending on your child’s
unique shape,
we have preemies, small, medium,
large, and extra large.
And not to worry, we have
diapers for boys and girls.
You can’t go wrong.
Joseph: In my day, picking
these out was a lot easier.
Joseph: Let’s see.
I know that she’s a girl,
and when I held her,
she was about this big,
give or take an inch.
Shopkeeper: When you held her?
I’m afraid I don’t follow you.
And I don’t want to run the risk
of you returning
ill-fitting soiled diapers.
I’m sure you can understand
the problem with that.
joseph: Yeah,
I completely understand.
Guess i’ll grab
every size you have.
In addition to that,
I need baby wipes,
instant formula,
and baby bottles.
Shopkeeper: Well, then,
you are in luck.
We carry both glass
and plastic baby bottles.
Glass bottles tend to be
scratch- and odor-resistant,
but can be heavy
for a baby’s arms to hold.
Plastic bottles may be light,
but they have
a tendency to trap odors.
Which of the two
would you like today?
Joseph: Uh, let’s see.
I guess i’ll take the one with--
shopkeeper: We also carry
an assortment
of shapes and designs.
We have rocket ships,
racing cars, and--
ooh, the baby could
hold this one by itself.
and when you
turn this one upside down,
the doll does
a delightful little dance.
It’s so adorable.
joseph:
Uh, I really don’t know,
so would you mind picking out
a few and calling it a day?
Shopkeeper: But you
haven’t seen our nipples.
The rubber ones
are soft and supple,
but they lack durability.
Silicone nipples are resilient,
but they tend to be so stiff.
This is our "choopa trainer."
There’s a diaphragm valve
in the nipple,
and when its coupled
with the baby’s
own suckling pressure,
it regulates the flow of milk
so the little one
gets the right amount.
this is the nuk,
a brand made in Germany.
It’s compressed into an oval
so the nipple can mimic
the mother’s natural shape.
And just as if the mother was
nursing the old-fashioned way,
the milk won’t flow
without the baby’s jaw movement.
joseph:
Oh, uh, i’m sure they’ll do.
I trust your judgment
on this stuff.
I’ll take them all.
We also carry nipple openings
in the circular, y-,
and cross-shaped varieties.
( Joseph grumbles )
Just give me everything.
And while you’re at it,
I need some baby clothes
and socks, too.
Oh, before I forget,
i’ll be paying by card.
shopkeeper:
Thank you very much, sir.
( Cash register rings )
Joseph: 136,000?
Now, what would the exchange
rate be in American dollars?
if i’m not mistaken,
you move the decimal point--
or rather,
100 yen is about 80 cents.
well, in any case,
it’s all for a good cause,
and it’s just
a bunch of baby stuff.
Really, how expensive
could a couple
of rug-rat essentials be?
Josuke: What is the holdup?
He’s taking forever.
We don’t have all day.
- Girl: By the way...
- Girl #2: Huh?
Girl #1: What happened with
the girl who got proposed to?
Does no reply mean
she’s not interested
or mulling things over?
Girl #2: I’d say the second one.
( Joseph gasps ) I can’t
take much more of this.
If someone from class sees me
here, it’s not gonna end well.
Joseph: Sorry to keep you
waiting, josuke.
- Here. Thanks for the loan.
- Josuke: Yeah, great.
Now let’s get going
while the getting’s good.
( Baby cooing )
josuke: Now we don’t
have to worry about losing her,
but there’s still a problem.
Without a face,
she’s gonna freak out everyone
she comes in contact with.
Joseph: I’m way ahead
of you, josuke.
I picked out some makeup
while I was at that store.
first she needs a dab
of foundation there and there.
Ugh!
( Baby cooing )
Josuke: Well, what do you know?
She’s actually pretty cute
when you can see her.
Joseph: Yeah, you’re right,
a vision of beauty.
Joseph: Good idea. This just
made finding her mother
a hell of a lot easier.
We might actually pull this off.
Consider me impressed.
Nice one, Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: I’m glad
I could help out.
Now then, it’s time we put on
the little lady’s lipstick.
a few strokes
for her brows and lashes,
a little here, and...
( Baby cooing )
Josuke: Why am I not surprised?
Toss a bit of flattery his way,
and the old man’s
walking on air.
Joseph: With your new makeover,
we can walk around without
attracting any attention.
And since we can’t
exactly powder your eyes,
sunglasses should do the trick.
( Baby cooing )
Joseph: Now she’s even cuter.
( Laughs )
josuke:
Here’s some milk for her.
Joseph: Hmm. Do you think I went
too light on the foundation?
It doesn’t seem
to be sticking to her.
Josuke: Huh? ( Gasps )
( Baby laughs )
Josuke: No, that’s not it.
Joseph: What the hell?
She’s fading out!
( Josuke gasps )
Joseph: She’s gone!
And my hands went with her!
Josuke: This is horrible!
she can make
other things invisible!
That means no solid object
is safe from her.
Joseph: Eh? What now?
Josuke: Mr. Joestar,
drop the baby!
Let go of it, damn it!
Hurry, before she
turns the rest of you.
( Baby crying )
Joseph: What? I let go,
but they’re still invisible.
Josuke: I think
she’s powering up.
( Baby crying )
( Both gasp )
( Thump )
Joseph: Uh...
Josuke: What are we
supposed to do?
anything that gets
within a 30-centimeter radius
of the baby is gonna be
turned completely invisible.
none of this
is making any sense.
She can’t be trying to protect
herself with her stand.
No one could take care of her
if she did.
something else
must be going on here.
Joseph: It seems like the effect
is triggered by anxiety.
- josuke: Eh?
- Joseph: Stress is the culprit.
Clearly, she doesn’t
like to be handled
by people she doesn’t know.
Josuke: And if she
powers up any more,
then no one
will be able to get near her.
We’ll end up invisible, too.
( Man humming a tune )
hmm?! Whoa,
what a weird heap of junk.
Someone better pick that up.
Oh, well, not my problem.
Someone else can do it.
Joseph: Yah! Look out.
( Clatter )
Josuke: Huh?
( Joseph groans )
Josuke: Hey, what happened?
joseph:
Somebody flicked a cigarette--
oh, you can’t see it.
( Both gasp )
Josuke: What the hell
are you doing, Mr. Joestar?!
Joseph: Huh?
josuke: Either get
with the program, old man,
or get out of the way!
Joseph: Oh, I didn’t know.
Sorry for the trouble.
( Baby wailing )
( Josuke gasps )
The stroller outright vanished,
and it took the ground with it.
He was right, it is stress.
The more she freaks out,
the stronger
her invisibility power gets.
- ( Clatter )
- Huh?
( Gasps )
Joseph: Tell me
I didn’t just hear
- the baby’s stroller flip over.
- ( Baby crying )
( Joseph gasps )
( Josuke gasps )
Are you for real?
The invisible baby
just fell in the water?
where is she?
Come on! Make some noise!
I don’t see any bubbles.
is she...
joseph: Josuke,
is there any sign of her?
- Josuke: Shut up!
- ( Joseph gasps )
Josuke: Every single horrible
thing that’s happened to me
today has been because
of this doddering old has-been.
how the hell is this
irresponsible jackass my father?
A man so careless he abandoned
my mom for 16 years.
i’ll never respect
a thoughtless bastard like him.
there’s no way
this was ever gonna work out.
Listen. Just stay out of this.
okay, she’s gotta
be around here somewhere.
I don’t care if you
turn me invisible, too.
Just touch me. Hurry.
Come on.
She’s not here. Damn it!
( Gasps ) Son of a--
how am I gonna find
an invisible baby,
especially when i’m waist-deep
in crystal-clear water?
Joseph: I’m truly sorry, josuke.
I won’t be able to hold out
long, so I have a request.
Tell your mom hello.
it’d mean the world
if you gave her my message.
Josuke: Huh?
Joseph: After all,
i’m just
a doddering old man, you know.
Josuke: What do you
think you’re doing?
Joseph: I’m giving the water
a little bit of color.
There, in the center.
Do you see it? The blood
disappears towards the middle.
That’s where the baby is.
Take care of her, josuke.
Josuke: Mr. Joestar.
( Baby crying )
♪
Josuke: No regular person
would even attempt
what you’ve just done,
not for a stranger’s kid
they’d only met that day.
You’re...
♪
( Chuckles )
joseph: Well, I just
wanted to look cool for you.
Tell me, did it work?
( Josuke groans )
well, that was
an experience i’ll never forget,
but, hey, all’s well
that ends well, I suppose. Huh?
( Gasps )
136,000 yen?!
My hard-earned money,
it’s all gone!
- You gray-haired douche!
- Joseph: There, there.
Huh?
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪