♪
Yoshihiro: Damn it all!
this is bad!
I have to let yoshikage know!
Koichi: It’s reimi!
Reimi: Hey, Rohan, did you
take the pictures in this album?
Rohan: I did. Why?
Reimi: I assume there’s a reason
this one is marked.
What’s so special about it?
You seem to have homed in
on this little boy.
Rohan: Oh, yeah.
I’m not too concerned with him.
he seemed to be
sneaking around the area,
so I thought i’d document him.
Reimi: But look.
The boy’s name
is hayato kawajiri.
He has the same surname
as this man.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Rohan: Really? He does?
Reimi: Yeah. Check it out.
weren’t you
investigating this person?
rohan: Mm-hmm. He was
one of many potential suspects.
( Yoshihiro shudders )
If Rohan kishibe
uncovers the truth,
it’s over
for my darling yoshikage!
Shinobu: Hayato? Hayato!
Damn it.
This is the last time
i’ll say it, hayato!
Answer me when I call you!
Oh, it’s you, dear.
Sorry for all the commotion.
i could have sworn
it was hayato in the bath.
Honestly, what are we
going to do with that boy?
Look at this place.
His clothes are scattered
around the hallway
like a bomb went off.
I wish he’d take after you
a little bit more.
He can be such a slob.
Not to mention he’s ignoring me.
Though, if I know him,
he’s probably reading manga
with his headphones on again.
( Gasps ) Honey, what happened?
You’ve got blood
on your fingers.
Let me take care of that.
You don’t want it
to get infected.
Eh? Eh?!
kira: No,
i’ll take care of it myself.
I just need a simple bandage.
I can handle that.
Shinobu: Oh. Uh...
Kira: I just caught
my fingers in the door.
It’s no big deal, really.
Shinobu: Ah.
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
josuke: Hayato kawajiri?
so you think
this grade-school kid
has something
to do with Kira?
Koichi: Well, at this point,
we’re not totally sure
if they’re connected.
That said, Rohan-sensei
thinks he’s onto something.
Josuke: I agree.
A grade-school kid
taking videos of his dad
on the down-low
sends up some serious red flags.
Koichi: We’re talking about
meeting up tomorrow morning.
Once we’ve gone through
everything, we’ll head over
to hayato kawajiri’s house
together.
Rohan-sensei said he’s already
figured out the address.
( Josuke chuckles )
that artsy asshole
doesn’t miss a beat, does he?
Josuke: Well, count me in.
Oh, and I should ask
okuyasu, right?
And jotaro, too.
Can’t forget about him.
Koichi: You can leave getting
in touch with Mr. Jotaro to me.
All right, we’ll see you
tomorrow at 8:30 A.M.
just look
for the big Pepsi sign.
Josuke: Right. Got it.
Pepsi at 8:30.
That means i’m gonna
be late for school.
Even so, if things pan out
the way Rohan hopes,
it’ll be worth the tardy slip.
♪
( Kira shudders )
Shinobu: Are you okay?
I can tell there’s
something wrong, sweetie.
You’re all pale and sweaty.
Kira: It’s nothing.
I’m perfectly fine.
I’m just in some pain, is all.
I did just slam my fingers.
Now please, go downstairs,
and make some tea.
I’ll be right behind you.
( Shinobu gasps )
( Sighs ) Okay, dear.
i know this is
gonna sound totally random,
but, well, I don’t know.
You’ve had this vibe,
like you’ll live forever.
( Kira shudders )
Shinobu: The tea’ll
be ready soon.
( Door creaks )
Yoshihiro: Huh?
( Kira shuddering )
Hayato: If you so much
as lay a single finger on me,
your whole cover
will be blown sky-high!
Stay the hell away
from me and my mom!
It’s non-negotiable.
You got that?!
stay away,
or I reveal everything!
Kira: You’re adorably naive!
As if i’d let
someone find me out!
- ( Trigger clicks )
- ( Boom )
Yoshihiro: Getting rid
of that hayato brat
was the very height
of foolishness.
You, of all people,
should have known that.
Kira: Quiet. I’m trying
to think of a way out of this.
Yoshihiro: Don’t waste time.
It’s too late for that now.
You did a remarkable job
of making it look
as though he fell
and hit his head,
but your timing
really couldn’t have been worse.
Rohan kishibe has already begun
his investigation
into hayato kawajiri.
They don’t know for sure yet
that kosaku kawajiri
is yoshikage Kira,
but they’re coming here tomorrow
to find out once and for all.
( Kira gasps )
Yoshihiro: Son,
you mustn’t remain
in this house a minute longer.
Kira: Will you stop talking?
I’m trying to think!
( Yoshihiro blubbers )
Even when you were a boy,
when things didn’t go your way
and you felt the world
was against you,
you’d always bite your nails
’til your fingers were raw.
( Kira murmuring )
Yoshihiro: My poor, sweet boy.
oh, the misery
you must be suffering.
we’ve run out
of options here, kiddo.
you must leave this
wretched town behind for good!
If you get out now,
you still have a chance
to escape and hold on
to your anonymity.
( Gasps )
Kira: Are you
seriously asking me
to run away and abandon morioh?!
living every moment
in excruciating secrecy is one
of the most horrible experiences
a person can go through,
and I refuse
to go back to that hell!
i swear I will
never leave this town.
( Yoshihiro gasps )
( Kira gasping )
What the hell?!
Yoshihiro: The arrow
moved on its own!
but I swear
I didn’t do anything!
I wasn’t even touching it!
Kira: Gah!
What’s it doing?
( Gasps )
Yoshihiro: No! Yoshikage!
( Kira gagging )
♪
Shinobu: Hayato! Hayato?!
just how long
are you gonna sleep in?
It’s time to get up and--eh?
Hayato, why didn’t you tell me
you were out of bed?
You startled me.
Come down for breakfast.
And answer when I call you.
hayato: I had
a terrible night’s sleep.
That jerkface imposter found out
I witnessed one of his murders
and assaulted me.
For now, i’ve made sure he can’t
do anything to hurt me or mom,
but that’s a temporary solution.
He’ll find a way around that.
- ( Kira humming a tune )
- ( Hayato gasps )
♪
Yoshihiro: I don’t understand.
what in the world’s
gotten into you, yoshikage?
You’ve been acting strange
since last night.
Don’t ignore me!
I don’t know why,
but Rohan kishibe
is now keen on snooping
around hayato kawajiri!
We’ve run out of time, son.
they’re coming
to search the house tomorrow!
( Kira chuckles )
There’s no cause for alarm.
Yoshihiro: B-but, yoshikage!
kira: My deadly queen
has acquired a third ability.
Yoshihiro: Huh?
What’s going on here?
♪
What could have happened
to make you
so lackadaisical
all of a sudden?
announcer:
...Miso-marinated cow tongue.
( Anchor coughs )
You’re kidding!
Why didn’t you say
we were on the air?!
Good morning, all. It’s 7:55,
time for today’s
prefectural weather report.
today we’ll be
enjoying sunny skies...
- ( Telephone rings )
- Shinobu: Hayato!
Hayato, are you listening?
Answer the phone!
( Telephone ringing )
Hayato: His attitude
has completely changed
since that bath last night.
what happened
between now and then?
( Telephone ringing )
Shinobu: Hayato,
what are you doing?
the damn phone isn’t
gonna answer itself, you know!
( Gasps )
( Shrieks )
My favorite China tea set!
( Hayato gasps )
Shinobu: This is
all your fault!
Why do you ignore me?!
Don’t you have any respect
for your mother?
Admit it! You only see me as
a nuisance who gets in the way!
Well, fine! I’m done!
- ( Hayato gasps )
- ( Telephone ringing )
Kira: Now, now.
Let’s not start the day
with an argument.
- hayato: Huh?
- Kira: If it can’t be fixed,
i’ll buy you another one.
This is the kawajiri residence.
No, i’m afraid not.
It was a wrong number.
that’s all.
and hayato’s
going through a quiet phase.
No need to fret.
( Hayato stammering )
Kira: We’re a family.
We should support each other,
not tear each other down.
Let’s all work on that.
Speaking of work,
I should get going.
But before I head off,
i’d like to steal a kiss.
( Shinobu gasps )
- Kira: Have a nice day.
- shinobu: Huh?
( Hayato gasps )
( Shinobu gasps )
Thank god. He took off.
Kira: No, i’m right here.
why don’t we
walk together for a bit?
( Hayato shuddering )
♪
one moment,
i’m in the throes of despair.
Now i’m on top of the world.
So much has happened
so very quickly.
It’s been an absolute
whirlwind of emotion.
But now, at long last,
i’ll be able
to live a life
free of worry and anxiety.
You really put the pressure on
last night,
but, because of you,
i’ve matured.
you were
so extraordinarily determined,
especially for a tyke your age.
It’s incredible that you
threatened yoshikage Kira.
Hayato: What? Yoshikage Kira?
( Kira laughs )
looks like
I just told you my name.
Hayato: D-does this mean
you’re gonna kill me after all?
Kira: Kill you? Simply because
you know my secret?
There’s no need for that.
Like I said, i’ve matured.
it doesn’t matter
what you or anyone else does.
No one in the world
can rival me now.
( Hayato gasps )
Kira: You no longer
arouse any interest in me,
and if I wanted to kill you,
I would have simply finished
the job last night.
We’re all going to get along
just fine. I guarantee it.
So take a breath, kiddo.
we’re family.
( Hayato shuddering )
Well, daddy dearest
is off to the station.
do your best
at school today, hayato.
Hayato: Huh?
( Thunder rumbling )
No one can rival him?
"Rival"? That means
there must be other people
walking around out there
with the same kind
of bizarre powers.
Still, his confidence
is terrifying.
he’s brazenly
calling himself unrivaled now.
does that mean
he gained some new power?
What do I do now?
Damn it. I have no idea
what i’m supposed to do.
♪
rohan: Hey,
you’re hayato kawajiri.
Hayato: Huh?
Rohan: Aren’t you?
Rohan: I’ve been
waiting for you.
My name is Rohan kishibe,
and I have a question for you.
Do us both a favor,
and answer it.
Hayato: Eh?
Rohan: It’s about this picture.
This is you, isn’t it?
And you were taking a video
of your dad
in the back there, right?
( Hayato gasping )
Rohan: Wait.
Hayato: What is this?
I know that was unexpected.
Questioning him
would be troublesome.
reading his mind
will be much more efficient
when it comes to this endeavor,
not to mention it’ll be far
more accurate than a q and a.
( Gasps )
Huh? Why would that
be in his pages?
The only thing heaven’s door
should be revealing is a candid,
honest written account
of this boy’s life memories,
and yet there’s a warning?
What’s going on?
This warning here, is it part
of the boy’s life experience?
When I drove over today,
I wasn’t planning on giving him
more than a quick peruse,
but now he’s got me
strangely hooked.
"Do not read on"? Hmm.
I wonder who could that be for?
( Gasps )
( Gasps ) What is all this?
This makes even less sense.
What does it mean?
( Man sneezes )
( Groans ) Damn it all.
( Rohan gasps )
( Women laugh )
This kid, who the hell is he?
Woman: Come on!
The weather report
never said anything about rain!
( Rohan gasping )
( Thunder rumbling )
No way. 8:27.
Who is this hayato kawajiri?
And how does he
experience the future?
Could he be a stand user?!
calm down.
No way this is a stand ability.
heaven’s door
can’t read the future.
it just reveals
what one has seen and heard.
I’m certain the explanation
would be somewhere
in these pages.
( Gasps )
Kira.
It’s all coming together.
This little kid, he’s a jackpot!
I finally found him!
Yoshikage Kira
is kosaku kawajiri!
He’s disguised himself
as this kid’s father!
( Chuckling )
Eh?
"Then Rohan kishibe
was also killed.
The new, superpowered Kira
found a way to murder him."
( Trigger clicks )
( Gasps )
Deadly queen: Deadly queen,
bomb type three, bites the dust.
Rohan: Heaven’s door, attack!
( Gasps )
Deadly queen: Deadly queen
has already entered
your pupil, Rohan kishibe!
No, you’re not seeing things!
Deadly queen’s bomb type three
has already been activated.
Your time has come!
( Rohan gagging )
♪
deadly queen:
And there you have it.
Deadly queen’s new power
will annihilate
all who attempt
to take me down!
It’s a bomb that will activate
in anyone who dares
approach hayato to get to me.
Hayato’s verbalizing
my true name
will also activate the bomb,
as will putting my name
in writing.
In other words, my new bomb
has been planted in hayato!
Rohan: I just remembered.
I promised to meet koichi.
He and the others
will be here at 8:30.
Excellent.
i’ve done it.
I rooted out yoshikage Kira.
I know who he is now.
Koichi will be here soon.
I have to let him know. I must.
( Gasps )
Over here.
I-I finally found him.
Yoshikage Kira
is kosaku kawajiri.
Heaven’s door sniffed him out.
You have to hear this.
Can you hear me? ( Gasping )
Koichi.
( Gasps )
deadly queen:
And now, gaze upon the glory
that is deadly queen,
bomb type three!
Rohan: K-koichi!
( Hayato screaming )
( Panting )
♪
W-was I dreaming?
I had a terrible night’s sleep.
It was one horrible dream
after another.
Shinobu: Hayato?!
just how long
are you gonna sleep in?
It’s time to get up and--eh?
Hayato, why didn’t you
tell me you were out of bed?
You startled me.
Come down for breakfast.
And answer when I call you.
( Hayato stammers )
I-it’s crazy, but I...
( Anchor coughs )
You’re kidding!
Why didn’t you say...
hayato: Wait!
I’ve seen this newscast!
( Telephone rings )
shinobu: Hayato!
Hayato, are you listening?
- ( Hayato gasps )
- Shinobu: Answer the phone!
Hayato: This isn’t a dream!
None of what just happened
was a dream.
This is the same morning!
Everything is repeating!
somehow i’m reliving
the same morning from yesterday!
Which means that guy’s real name
is yoshikage Kira!
He’s behind all this!
This is what he meant
by being unrivaled.
He’s done something to me
with his new power!
Shinobu: Hayato,
what are you doing?
the damn phone isn’t
gonna answer itself, you know!
( Hayato gasps ) Oh, yeah!
( Shinobu gasps )
Hayato: Watch it!
Kira: Hmm?
- ( Telephone ringing )
- shinobu: Ow.
Huh? Nice catch, hayato.
It’s almost like you knew
I was going to drop it.
But you could try
answering me next time!
Hello. Kawajiri residence.
- Huh? No, wrong number.
- Hayato: So i’m the only one
who knows this morning
already happened.
For everyone else,
it’s business as usual.
Kira: It’s like you knew
she was going to drop it, eh?
( Chuckles )
It appears you’ve returned
from a long day
of blasting your friend
to kingdom come, hayato.
truthfully,
i’m not actually privy
to all the gory details
of your little foray today,
but deadly queen’s new power
is called "bites the dust."
It automatically protects me
from right inside your body,
so thank you, hayato.
( Hayato gasps )
Kira: Tell me,
are you even aware
that I killed you last night
when we were in the bath?
At that moment, it was as if
the fates themselves
had witnessed my despair
and I was granted a gift
in the form of this ability.
I tried the ability out on you,
and miraculously
time reversed course one hour.
The reality that i’d
murdered you was no more.
At the same time,
you also became my personal
life-protecting bomb.
You told one of them about me,
thereby activating the bomb
and sending you back here.
So who did you annihilate, hmm?
I won’t tell.
Who did you murder?
Hayato: No, you’ve got it wrong.
I didn’t tell anyone anything.
( Kira laughs ) Of course not!
Which tells me
you were interrogated
by Rohan kishibe, no doubt.
Even if you never think
about tattling,
a simple inquiry
into the identity of yours truly
will be enough to activate
the horrors of bites the dust.
After which, you’ll incinerate
the offender and zip back here.
Your visit with Rohan kishibe
is now a figment
of your imagination.
so now you know
the power of bites the dust.
my true name
will never cross your lips,
and no soul will live
long enough to seek me out.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪