Jotaro: Josuke...
I’m going on a hunting trip.
Josuke: Huh?
Jotaro: And you’re coming, too.
Josuke: Eh, whoa there!
Hang on a second, jotaro.
Run that by me again.
I could have sworn you said
we were going hunting.
If that’s true,
does that mean
we’re going hunting
for hotties with hot bodies?
’cause you should know
i’m a little more
of the romantic type.
i’m not sure
i’ll be able to pull it off.
You’ll have to show me
the ropes.
Jotaro: I spoke to otoishi.
He confessed.
Josuke: Are you serious?
jotaro: Yeah,
he had quite a lot to say,
especially regarding
the bow and arrow.
It turns out he also used it
to shoot a rat.
Josuke: He did what?!
Jotaro: That’s right,
but the rat didn’t die.
Even though it was
writhing in agony,
it freed itself from the arrow
and made a break for the hills.
( Josuke gasps )
Jotaro: You know
what that means.
Humans aren’t the only organisms
with the potential
to acquire stand abilities,
but we don’t know
what this rat can do,
so we have to hunt it down
before it lashes out.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Josuke: Whoa, that was awesome!
Jotaro: Those were
just regular cans.
keeping a nimble rat
within range won’t be so easy,
which is why we have
these bearings.
They’ll expand your range
to 20 meters.
This should be obvious, but
they’re useless against stands.
Use them when you’re in position
to take down the user.
Give it a try.
Josuke: I have to use ’em, too?
You sure about this?
I don’t even have
the concentration
for ball sports
and stuff, you know?
( Groans ) I almost got it.
Jotaro: Not bad for a newbie.
I’d give it an 85.
But I need you to remember
one thing while on this hunt.
When dealing with live animals,
you have to prioritize
composure over speed.
If you corner the rat
and screw up the shot,
don’t expect it
to be gullible enough
to come within range again,
so hold your fire until you
know you can hit your target.
One more thing.
Don’t let the pressure
bog you down. Got it?
Josuke: Wow, he sure knows
how to make a guy feel at ease.
Jotaro: From what he told me,
otoishi shot the rat
near this irrigation canal.
given the location,
it was probably a brown rat.
Brown rats are agile swimmers,
adaptable, and can eat
practically anything.
larger rats can grow
up to 20 or 30 centimeters long,
and some can weigh
as much as one kilogram,
with a horizontal leap
of about two meters.
- Found them.
- Josuke: Huh?
you mean
those aren’t bird tracks?
Its forefeet have four digits
and its hind feet five.
The "s" shape means
it’s dragging something.
These markings are tail tracks.
the rat’s
about 20 centimeters long.
I don’t know how many, but there
more than one here. Huh?
There’s a tick on this leaf,
which means it’s
a stomping ground for rodents.
♪
There’s no question about it.
Somewhere in that drain
is a nest.
For now, our best bet
is to set a trap
and see what
the video camera picks up.
josuke: Huh?
That’s one of those cameras
that lets you watch
while you’re recording, right?
Uh, you’re not gonna use cheese
for the trap? ( Sniffs )
Jotaro: It’s a hunk of tempura.
Cheese is too luxurious
for a common rat.
- ( Flies buzzing )
- Josuke: Eh?
What’s with all the flies?
Did something die?
( Gasps ) Jotaro!
Th-these are--( Gags )
Jotaro: Hmm? ( Gasps )
Those are dead rats.
Josuke: Yeah, no shit.
( Groans )it looks like
a block of jellied fish.
Why the hell are you poking it?
Jotaro: It’s flesh.
at some point,
the flesh of these rats melted
and later congealed.
It seems as though the melting
started from under their flesh.
Josuke: How in the world
does something as messed up
as that even happen?
Jotaro: Don’t know.
If I had to guess,
i’d say this is the handiwork
of the rat we’re after.
Josuke: So its stand did this?
Jotaro: That seems
to be the case.
It took out its fellow rats
to seize the territory,
which would mean
it’s highly likely
the rat’s making a nest
in that drain.
The question now is,
has our culprit used its powers
to wreak any more havoc?
Looks like the drainage canal
continues on to that house.
We might already be too late.
Josuke: You think
it beat us here?
Jotaro: At first glance,
I see a chicken Coop,
but no chickens.
The cars are still parked
in the garage,
and there doesn’t appear to be
any activity in that house.
The front door
is unlocked and open.
all signs point
to the rat being inside.
It’s safe to assume
the owners of this house
have already been killed.
let’s go.
We have to investigate.
The rat will let us approach it
up to a certain point.
It’s intelligent enough to know
that most humans are too slow
to ever catch it,
so it’s not expecting
to be used as target practice.
That’s how we’ll close in
and put an end to this mess
with one shot.
- Bingo.
- Josuke: Eh?
Jotaro: These are rat droppings.
There’s no grass or grain here,
only meat.
The droppings lead to that room.
- Come on.
- Josuke: Right.
- ( Motor whirring )
- uh...
what? It looks like
an old refrigerator compressor.
What the hell? Am I going crazy,
or did the refrigerator
just open by itself?
Did the door’s magnet
give out or something?
- ( Rat chewing )
- Josuke: Holy shit, I found it!
That little bastard’s
right there!
I get it. So that’s
what opened the fridge.
nobody told me rats
could open refrigerator doors.
That doesn’t make any sense.
Someone must have
forgotten to shut it.
No. Get real, josuke.
You’re not that gullible,
are you?
This rat’s a stand user.
Jo--
( gasps ) That’s right.
Jotaro went into the next room
to look for the rat.
( Gasps )
Freakin’ great.
Now our eyes have met.
( Victims groaning )
Josuke: How the hell...
The rat did this?
( Gasps ) They’re still alive.
Did the rat disfigure
the owners of this house
with its stand
so it’d have an easier time
storing them in the fridge?
Oh, and it’s eating them!
damn it.
Jotaro’s not coming back.
I’ll have to kill
this thing myself.
When dealing with live animals,
you have to focus
on composure over speed.
If I don’t tag him
on my first try,
he’ll know my range.
Damn it, jotaro.
I know you said no pressure,
but still...
Of course the table and chair
are positioned just enough
to be in my way.
I have to make sure
I sink this ball bearing
right between
his beady little eyes.
Now stay right there.
Oh, crap. He stopped eating.
If I move closer,
he’ll run for it.
Forget this. It’s now or never.
I’ll blast him from over here.
He’s moving! Now!
- I got it!
- ( Rat squeals )
( Hisses )
josuke: Shit.
It wasn’t a fatal blow.
( Rat roars )
Josuke: Here we go.
That weird machine
must be his stand.
All right, pal,
come and get some
if you think you’ve got
what it takes to beat me.
Just know that my next shot
is gonna take you out for good.
damn it!
He’s running under the table!
No, you don’t!
Jotaro, what the hell
are you doing?!
The rat’s in here! ( Gasps )
That shape.
Not good!
His stand fires projectiles!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Josuke: What now?
Should I slap it away
with my bare hands?
No, that’s disgusting.
Where’s the rat?
did I hit it with
my ball bearing, or did I miss?
( Rat squeals )
( Josuke gasps ) You bastard.
( Rat shrieks )
Josuke: Yeah!
I got him after all!
It wasn’t between his eyes like
I said, but he’s still a goner.
That was a close one.
( Sighs )
Hey, jotaro, get over here!
I took out the rat!
The hunt is over.
Jeez, what were
you doing in there?
You went missing right
when I needed you the most.
I was starting to think
you’d abandoned me.
But, hey, at least it’s dead.
Luckily everything
went according to plan.
Well, for me, that is.
Our rat friend
wasn’t so fortunate.
though his stand shot
some needle-like things at me.
Whatever they were,
I bet they’re what
turn your flesh to goo.
He got to the people
who own this place,
but they’re still alive.
I’ll fix ’em right up
with shining diamond.
Jotaro: If we don’t
eliminate him by sundown,
things might get even messier.
Josuke: Huh?
Jotaro: There was another rat,
and that one managed to hit me.
( Josuke gasps )
Jotaro, your hand is melting!
Jotaro: It happened
in the other room.
I could have dodged the attack,
but I thought catching
the needle for analysis
was the best choice.
All it takes is a touch,
and its stand’s poison
begins to permeate,
even melting other stands.
Five or six hits,
and you’ll turn into
a quivering mass of flesh.
Josuke: Ohh! Good thing
that needle didn’t hit me.
Never thought i’d be grateful
for being squeamish.
Jotaro: The rat
bolted out the door
after hitting me
with the needle.
Somehow it must have figured out
you killed its kin
here in the kitchen.
Um, sorry to bother,
but would you mind using
your power to fix my hand?
Josuke: Uh, not to worry.
Just leave it to me.
damn it. Why’d those
little s.O.B.S have to multiply?
Man: This is the speedwagon
foundation research department.
jotaro: Hello.
This is jotaro kujo speaking.
Man: Jotaro! Finally.
We’ve tried to reach you
several times.
Jotaro: I was hunting the rat
and had the ringer off.
Is this about otoishi?
Man: Yes. Akira otoishi
was withholding the fact
that he shot two rats
instead of one.
Jotaro: Are you sure?
is there any chance he
could have shot three or four?
Man: No, sir.
We’re sure it’s two.
Jotaro: Oh, good grief, otoishi.
What a fool.
when it comes
to its own territory,
it’ll kill everything,
humans and rats alike.
It cares only about itself.
So this savage’s time on earth
is about to come to a fast end.
Let’s move.
josuke: Jotaro,
hold on a minute, would you?
a pint-sized rodent
just ran into an open field.
How exactly do you plan
on tracking this thing down?
Jotaro: The famous artist
Ernest Thompson seton once said
there’s not an animal
on the planet
that cannot be tracked.
You have to know their habits.
rats are known
to avoid unfamiliar paths,
which means its route of escape
had to be that
irrigation channel from before.
And there’s something else
about rats.
if they’re
not constantly eating,
they’ll starve
within a few hours.
there.
Those are fresh bite marks.
Josuke: Nice going.
This is an awesome start.
Now we’re gonna corner
that bucktoothed bastard!
( Sighs ) Take a look at this.
I don’t think he even gave
a damn that our bait was here.
Jotaro: He’s on tape.
Huh. His ear looks
like a bug-eaten leaf.
what do you say
we call him "bug-eaten"?
He’s being cautious.
This isn’t gonna be
like at the house.
Bug-eaten is gonna
be extra careful
to not let us get
within 20 meters of him.
These are live rifle rounds.
Worst-case scenario, we’ll have
to use these to finish the job.
Josuke: Wait. Those are real?
Jotaro: Yeah, they have to be.
Because of air resistance,
ball bearings lose accuracy
when traveling over 20 meters.
With a bullet nose like this,
we’ll be able to hit our Mark
up to 70 meters away.
Josuke: Will I
have to launch that
with my stand’s hand, too?
’cause I don’t think
i’m ready for that just yet.
Jotaro: Point taken.
I’ll have to be
the one to do it.
Josuke: Hold it right there.
Just what are you trying to say?
that comment
didn’t sit well with me.
I am the one who nailed the rat
back at the house, remember?
Sure, it wasn’t exactly
a perfect shot, but still...
Jotaro: Guess you’re right.
Take two.
Josuke: Huh? ( Groans )
( Groans ) More pressure.
♪
( Gasps )
( Gasping )
Jotaro: Be careful.
This puddle is full of leeches.
Josuke: Wha?!
( Sobs )
( Jotaro gasps ) Shit.
Josuke: So what’s going on?
Jotaro: Be careful. Eyes up.
The footprints
suddenly stop here.
Josuke: You’ve gotta be joking.
why would they
randomly stop like that?
I know. He’s under us.
He must have burrowed a hole
and covered himself.
Jotaro: No.
This is called backtracking.
I didn’t know rats
could do this, too.
Josuke: Backtracking?
Narrator: Backtracking is
the way in which a wild animal
reverses itself
by stepping in its own tracks.
This confuses predators
long enough for them to hide.
In Japan, the behavior
has been observed
with brown bears,
weasels, and rabbits.
However, it is unheard of
among rats and other rodents.
josuke: Okay,
so let me get this straight.
you’re saying
that a common brown rat
pulled a fast one on us?
Jotaro: Things have taken
a turn for the worse.
With this kind of terrain,
the hunters may have
just become the prey.
( Stand clicking )
Josuke: I have this creepy
feeling we’re being watched.
We better duck behind a rock
while we still have the chance.
Jotaro: No sudden movements.
the good news
is bug-eaten’s attack
isn’t too fast for us to see.
Just keep an eye out
for the point of fire.
If we can figure out
where he’s hiding,
we’ll snipe him instead.
( Josuke gasps )
( Yelps ) Son of a bitch!
( Groaning )
That dirty rodent used
our own rattrap against us?
Jotaro: Star platinum,
the world!
( Clock ticking )
- ( Ticking stops )
- Oh, good grief.
( Josuke yelps )
( Gasping )
Jotaro: Don’t worry.
I removed the needle
before the poison spread,
along with all
the affected tissue.
You should put a bandage on it.
I was also able to locate
his general whereabouts.
take a look.
He’s halfway up the hill,
near those three rocks.
josuke:
You found him and helped me?
i don’t know who’s
more amazing, you or the rat.
Compared with the two of you,
it’s starting to feel like i’m
a kid at the grownups’s table.
Jotaro: It’s 60 meters away.
So far, no sign
of any more needles.
He knows a random firing
would give away his location,
and its obvious
he doesn’t want to be attacked.
He’s a stubborn bastard.
Jotaro: Why are you
praising that damn rat?
we need to act,
and we have to do it now.
Jotaro: Well spoken, josuke.
We need to give this assault
everything we’ve got,
or bug-eaten’ll kill us both.
All right, i’ll give you
all four rounds.
at this distance,
the rounds’ll rise like sliders,
so aim one centimeter
below the target.
Josuke: If i’m firing,
what are you gonna do?
Jotaro: I’m moving in
so he’ll shoot his needles.
your job, josuke,
is to determine his location.
Then i’m counting on you
to end this.
( Josuke gasps )
You want me to what?!
Jotaro: You don’t have
a choice in the matter.
Even if one or two
of his needles get me,
you can just use
shining diamond to heal me.
You can’t heal yourself
with that power,
so you get the kill shot.
♪
This is our last stand.
Make it count.
( Josuke groans )
could I have
a second to prepare?
jotaro:
Star platinum, the world!
( Clock ticking slows )
Did you find him?
Josuke: No. As soon as he fired,
he ran off
and hid somewhere else.
Jotaro: I’ll try getting closer
while going up
the side of the hill.
Wait for him to fire.
Josuke: Yeah, will do.
Damn this pressure.
( Gasps )
There! I see him!
( Groans )
What the--that little shit-heel
predicted i’d dodge his attack
and fired the needles
at the rocks instead.
They ricocheted at me.
( Groans )
Josuke: Jotaro, no!
Jotaro: Don’t stand there
gawking at me, josuke!
Keep your eyes
trained on the rat.
the moment he attacks,
blow his ass straight to hell!
Josuke: This isn’t good.
I’ve got four rounds,
but i’m out of chances.
if I waste
even a single second...
Jotaro: Here we go, josuke.
Josuke: There!
He’s in the same spot
as the last time he fired,
but he’s hiding
behind the rocks.
Shit! If only he was
looking over here.
( Jotaro groans )
Josuke: I’ve gotta do this.
I’ll just have to hit
a tiny target.
No problem.
I suddenly feel
that fighting spirit.
right, then.
It’s time for you to die.
( Bug-eaten squeals )
Jotaro: Josuke missed.
What do we do now?
( Bug-eaten squealing )
♪
Josuke: There you are.
i knew my miss
would make you turn around.
It’s good to see
that ugly face.
and right now,
you’re right in my crosshairs.
( Bug-eaten shrieking )
Josuke: Guess I can hang
with the grown-ups after all.
Call me josuke higashikata,
the mighty vanquisher
of pressure and stress!
Jotaro: Akira’s mutant
stand rats got me thinking.
They’re reflections of our
destruction of the environment.
I’m not sure how to feel.
but at least
josuke’s a dependable guy.
Good grief.
Maybe now we’ll all get
a little peace of mind.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪