Hayato: You’re done!
Nothing you’ve got
compares to these guys’s
righteous hearts!
They’re gonna make you pay!
Can you feel it, yoshikage Kira?
The truth is staring you
right in the face!
You’re nothing compared to them!
( Kira gasping )
♪
( Gasping )
This has to be a bad dream.
There’s no other explanation.
things like this
just don’t happen to me.
It’s impossible.
such an outrage
would befall me only in a dream.
Okuyasu: Nah,
it’s the real deal,
and you’re goin’ down!
Josuke: I guess this means
your good fortune’s run out!
hayato:
You’re through, murderer.
Koichi: Look. Josuke’s been
clobbered to a bloody mess.
Rohan: Given the state
of his injuries,
it seems they’ve been battling
a little while now,
which means we’re looking at--
jotaro: The one and only,
yoshikage Kira.
( Kira shuddering )
Woman: We have
a bleeder over here!
Someone bring over an ambulance,
and get a stretcher now!
- Sir, can you hear me?
- Man: Get back!
- Hey, I said get back!
- Woman: If you can hear me,
there’s an ambulance
on the way.
rest assured
you’re in very good hands!
- ( Hayato gasps )
Don’t do it! Get away from her!
Woman: We’ll be taking you
to the hospital momentarily.
Just stay with me, all right?
( Gasps ) Don’t worry.
You’ll be fine.
( Both gasp )
Hayato: No! We were too slow!
kira’s already turned
that medical lady into a bomb!
( Both gasp )
( All gasp )
Woman: How many fingers
am I holding up?
Rohan: Jotaro, it’s time
to use star platinum.
Jotaro: I’m well aware,
but i’m not close enough
for it to be effective.
at this distance,
stopping time is useless.
He’s too far away to damage.
I need to get at least
five meters closer to him.
Josuke: So he’s gonna hold
her hostage as a human bomb.
Go ahead, and blow her up
if you’re so bad!
I’ll fix her faster than you
can say, "deadly queen"!
Hayato: Josuke,
just keep your cool!
Kira blowing up the hostage
is the least of our worries!
I couldn’t tell you before,
but he’s been hiding
a secret power!
It’s called bites the dust,
and he can use it
to obliterate time!
( All gasp )
His ability manifests itself
with non-stand users,
normal people
like me and that lady.
That’s why I couldn’t talk to
you guys in the other timelines.
it only appears
when Kira screws the pooch
and runs out of options!
That’s the exact situation
we’re in right now!
he’s spiraling into
the deepest pits of despair,
so he’s made a bomb that
turns back time by one hour!
josuke: This day
just keeps getting worse!
( Kira gasping )
It’s so beautiful.
your elegant hand,
its silky-smooth knuckles,
and your supplely soft skin.
it’s so pure,
i’d even call it milky.
May I use your gorgeous hand
to caress my cheek?
Woman: Huh?
Kira: It soothes my soul
and brings relief
to my restless spirit.
- ( Moaning )
- ( Woman shuddering )
( Kira sighs )
When I was a young boy,
I remember discovering
Leonardo da vinci’s
enigmatic Mona Lisa
while leafing through a Tome
of the master’s works.
( Shudders )
It was my first time
laying eyes on her.
The beauty before me,
well, it aroused
something in me. ( Chuckles )
It gave me a rock-hard [beep]
( Woman gulps )
Kira: I cut off her hands
and proudly displayed
the treasures in my room.
Now I lust to sever
your treasures.
- ( Moans )
- Woman: Sir, please!
What do you think
you’re doing?!
Kira: The truth is,
my name is yoshikage Kira.
i’ve had the pleasure
of killing 48 beautiful women
with even more beautiful hands.
But you’re a special beauty!
You will be the only one to have
ever known my true identity.
Hayato: Guys, this isn’t good!
Bites the dust
is about to activate!
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Hayato: Quickly!
We have to kill him right now!
If we let Kira live,
everyone here besides her
will be blown to smithereens!
( All gasp )
Koichi: Jotaro!
( Josuke growls )
( Winces )
Kira: What’s this, jotaro?
My hatred for you fools
has manifested bites the dust,
and you’re
charging ahead anyway?
If that’s how you want it!
You can stop time
for all I care!
In fact, all I want is for you
to back me into a corner!
Once i’m pushed to the brink,
my stand’s power
will be triggered,
and i’ll put you cretins
out of commission permanently!
Josuke: Jotaro,
stop time, already!
You can’t let him push
deadly queen’s switch!
( Woman gasps ) What’s going on?
kira: I’ve finally
reached my limit with you all!
- Time to die!
- ( Switch clicks )
Yes! I succeeded!
I activated it!
( Birds chirping )
Kira: Eh?
Hmm?
- ( Wings fluttering )
- ( Gasps )
( Sighs )
( Chuckling )
( Laughs )
I made it back safely.
I actually pulled it off!
I was able to activate
bites the dust yet again!
( Laughs )
I destroyed the interlopers!
At last, my quiet life
of freedom can begin!
( Laughs )
( Gasps )
Hmm?
Is my mind playing tricks?
Those birds flew
right through me.
But that’s absurd.
♪
Something isn’t right.
Like this street,
i’ve never once
used it to get to work.
Time was reversed by one hour,
so I should be on my way
to the office.
What the devil is going on?
where am I?
And, for that matter, when?
Huh? Oh, that’s right.
I put my watch
in my breast pocket
after I burned my wrist.
Huh? It can’t be!
Why is the watch still broken?!
And the time, it says 8:29!
there’s no way.
I activated bites the dust!
this is the watch
hayato broke with stray cat.
It should have returned
to its undamaged state!
reimi:
Still don’t get it, do you?
Kira: Huh?
Eh? ( Gasps )
Reimi: Well, well,
the kosaku kawajiri
in rohan’s photo
was really yoshikage Kira.
so then,
the battle’s finally over.
amazing.
The great yoshikage Kira
bested by those he’d spit upon.
Kira: And who the hell
are you, girl?
Reimi: You forgot
about little ol’ me?
Typical. I should have known.
Though it did happen
15 years ago.
Kira: Huh?
Reimi: Something truly horrible
must have happened to you
in the end,
something so harrowing,
you’ve lost any and
all recollection of what it was.
Kira: Are you
another stand user,
you talkative little tart?!
reimi: No,
i’m the bearer of bad news.
You’ve been sent to this place,
because you bit it, bub!
Kira: I--what?
♪
( Gasping )
( Screams )
Reimi: Understand now?
This is no stand ability!
This is proof, proof that
there’s justice in this world
and your murderous soul
will rot until the end of time!
- ( Kira screaming )
- Reimi: How ’bout it?
Have I jogged your memory?
Do you remember how you died?
♪
Jotaro: I can’t stop time now.
He’s too far away.
josuke:
Don’t let him do it, jotaro!
Kira: I’ve finally reached
my limit with you all.
Time to die!
( Gasps )
Reverb: Mission success!
The primary target has entered
the five-meter active range
of act three! Three freeze!
S-h-i-t!
( Kira gasps )
( Groaning )
release me,
you insignificant pest!
Jotaro: Star platinum,
unleash the world!
( Clock ticks )
♪
( Chorus vocalizing )
Koichi, you’re the most reliable
guy i’ve ever met.
I’ll be forever grateful
that I was able to come here
and get to know you.
Good grief, though.
That was a close call,
but we made it!
♪
Star platinum: Ora!
( Jotaro inhales )
( Yelling )
Jotaro: That’s enough. Time in.
( Kira gagging )
( Both gasp )
Josuke: Hey, he did it!
Hayato: Man, that was close!
Kira: You haven’t beaten me.
I’ll push that button,
and, when I do, bites the dust
will hunt you all down.
This is far from over.
( Woman gasps ) But how?
He just flew into the air!
Kira: I’ll push that button.
Just wait and see.
I’ll blow you to hell.
If I do, I can live out
my days in peace and quiet.
Rohan: His tenacity
is certainly impressive.
( Both sigh )
- Man: Hey, stop!
- ( Both gasp )
Man: Stop!
You’re gonna run over this guy!
( Woman screams )
Josuke: Oh, shit!
( Koichi wails )
( Hayato gasps )
( Woman and man scream )
Mbulance
just ran over that man!
Man 2: He came out of nowhere!
man 1: Move!
Pull forward, damn it!
Officer: All right, you two,
i need you
to get behind the tape!
Officer 2: Get back!
Come on! Get back!
Man 3: I need you
to just lie down.
( Josuke sighs )
Man 2: There’s
nothing we can do.
It was an instantaneous death.
( Woman sighs )
( Hayato gasps )
( Rohan gasps )
Okuyasu: He’s dead?
Man 1: It’s so crazy.
it’s like he tried
to dive under the ambulance.
woman: I feel
responsible for this.
I know there’s no excuse
for what happened,
but I didn’t have a chance
to restrain him.
Jotaro: Life can be bizarre.
man 2: He was pinned
between the asphalt and tire.
The force tore off his face.
( Officer 1 clears throat )
do we know
the identity of the victim?
Woman: He was yoshikage Kira.
He told me his name himself.
- ( All gasp )
- Officer 1: Kira.
There’s an old house in kotodai
belonging to the Kira family.
I heard there was
only one occupant,
so he might not have family.
Koichi: An accident.
To think an accident
would end this.
rohan: It all
worked out for the best.
The law would never
have been able to give
the punishment he deserved.
There was no better outcome.
Hayato: I-I never really
got along with my dad
when he was still with us,
but, even so,
I never thought i’d lose him.
I wanted justice
for my dad’s death.
i wanted someone
to bring his killer to justice.
( Kira screams )
Reimi: Remember now,
yoshikage Kira?
That’s how your life
was ripped away from you.
Funny how memory works!
kira: I’ve had
just about enough of your games!
Who or what are you?!
Reimi: I’m evidence.
15 years ago,
you didn’t have a stand
that could make
all of your victims disappear.
That’s why, when I was murdered,
it was front-page news.
( Kira gasps )
reimi: Tell me,
does this gash on my back
look familiar to you?
since I was
your very first victim,
maybe you forgot
to cut off my hands!
i guess i’m just
not that memorable to you, huh?
Kira: That’s right. It’s you.
of course.
You’re reimi sugimoto.
Tell me right now what you’ve
been planning here
for the past 15 years!
Huh?
Hold on.
What exactly do you get
out of showing off
your disgusting wound
and revealing
your true identity to me?
Now wait just a moment.
Is this the place
where one shouldn’t look
over their shoulder or else?
( Reimi gasps )
Kira: My old man once said,
hidden somewhere in this town
is a passage
for the souls of the dead.
He told me to never look back
if I ever found myself there.
To do so would invite
an unspeakable power
that would drag you
into an abyss of misery.
- ( Reimi gasps )
- Kira: Now, it’s just a hunch,
but I get the feeling
you only showed me your back
in order to lure me
in front of you
so i’d play
into your ghostly hands
and turn around.
( Reimi gasps )
Kira: You were
trying to trick me,
weren’t you,
my spectral strumpet?
Why don’t you look for me? Hmm?
I would love to see
what happens.
Now let’s have us a look.
Turn that pretty little head!
Reimi: Oh, please.
Did you think
I wouldn’t prepare for you
pulling a stunt like this?
- ( Kira gasps )
- Reimi: You’re so predictable.
We’ve been waiting for 15 years.
that was way more
than enough time to prepare.
Kira: "We"?
( Arnold growls )
Reimi: Yeah! Good boy, Arnold!
( Kira yelps )
( Gasps )
♪
What?! ( Screams )
Reimi: Yoshikage Kira, your hour
of reckoning has arrived.
kira: Disgusting!
What are these putrid things?
Deadly queen!
Make whatever this is explode!
Oh, god, no.
Where are they
going to take me?!
Say something, please!
i have to know
where they’re taking me!
What are they going to do?!
Reimi!
Reimi: Don’t know. Although...
I doubt you’ll be living
in peace and tranquility.
( Kira screams )
♪
Reimi: Now, at long last,
we can finally pass on together.
Koichi: What?! Are you
really leaving us, reimi?
Surely it wouldn’t hurt anything
if you stayed
a little while longer.
I mean, you’ve been like
a guardian angel to this town.
I can’t imagine
life here without you!
Please, you have to stay!
Reimi: Koichi,
you’re very sweet,
but Arnold and I have done
everything we set out
to accomplish here.
the time’s come
for us to leave morioh.
That’s how it has to be.
so, little Rohan,
do you think you’re gonna cry
after we’ve gone off
to the great beyond?
( Rohan chuckles )
In your dreams.
what reason
would I have to miss you?
You died 15 years ago,
making you a distant memory.
I’ve said this before,
but spirits
should really just let go.
Haunting the world of the living
is so out of style.
A soul’s final resting place
isn’t here with us,
but exploring
the uncharted afterlife.
( Koichi groans )
Rohan: Uh, hmph.
( Koichi growling )
( Rohan sighs )
Fine! I’ll say it, all right?!
But i’m only doing so because
i’ll never see you again!
- I’ll miss you!
- ( Koichi laughs )
Rohan: Of course
I don’t want you to go!
( Reimi chuckles )
( Arnold whimpers )
Josuke: Yo.
Koichi: Hey! You’re all here!
Yukako: So it’s all over, reimi?
koichi: Oh, wow!
Looks like everyone showed up!
Mikitaka: We’ve all
come to say goodbye.
♪
( Reimi gasps )
You guys.
josuke:
It feels weird to say this
to the dearly departed,
but take care of yourself.
okuyasu: See you
on the other side, ’kay?
( Mr. Nijimura gurgles )
Joseph: You’re an extraordinary
young woman, dear.
( Reimi whimpers )
Koichi: Oh, reimi,
thank you so much
for all you’ve done!
You saved this little town when
it needed a savior the most!
reimi: Thank you
for saying that, koichi,
but we saved morioh,
all of us together.
Joseph: As long
as we draw breath,
no one here today will ever
forget you or your bravery.
Reimi: Thank you, all.
That means the world.
So long, my friends. Be well.
( Rohan sighs )
Koichi: So long, reimi.
Godspeed.
Rest easy.
Shinobu: Where is he?
it’s so late.
I guess he’s working overtime.
It would have been nice
if he called, though.
( Hayato gasping )
shinobu: Oh, hayato,
you haven’t touched your food.
hurry up
before it gets cold.
If you’re waiting for me,
i’ll eat when dad gets home.
( Hayato gasping )
Shinobu: Uh, hayato?
Hayato: It’s okay, mom.
I’ll wait with you.
When dad gets home, we’ll all
sit down and eat together,
’cause that’s
what a family does, right?
Shinobu: Sure.
Say, am I imagining things,
or have you
gotten taller lately?
Koichi: When all
was said and done,
our little morioh
wasn’t the town it used to be.
A monster named yoshikage Kira
swept in like a plague
and had his way
with our beloved home.
Hayato’s mother will no doubt
wait for her husband
until the end of time,
and shigechi’s parents
will never stop waiting
for their special
little man to return.
Whether a son, daughter,
brother, or sister,
kira’s victims belong to parents
who will never give up hope,
and yet that hope
will only cause their pain
to grow deeper.
The question is, what can
we do to lessen this burden?
Will a vile past
consume our future,
or will we be able to forge
ahead, unfettered by fear?
I wish I could say.
Joseph: How ’bout it, jotaro?
You worried about
what might happen
when we leave this place?
Jotaro: I am, just a bit.
Joseph: Because of all this,
we’ve had the chance
to see how capable
josuke and his friends are,
and there’s one thing I can say
with absolute certainty.
The young people
living in this town
are heroes one and all,
and each one of them
possesses a heart of gold.
They’ve the same
righteous hearts
we witnessed
on our journey to Egypt.
They carry a spirit of radiance
that will fight for true justice
above all else.
I see it in josuke,
as well as the others.
Morioh’s in good hands
with them.
As long as they’re here,
we have nothing to worry about.
Josuke: Hey, old man!
Don’t just stand there gawkin’!
Answer me!
Joseph: Well, then, guess it’s
time for me to say goodbye
to a great son who’s made
his father so very proud.
Josuke: Hey, remember
that picture of mom
I gave you a while ago?
You don’t still have it,
do you?
Joseph: ’course I do!
I put it in my wallet
for safekeeping,
just like you told me to! Hah!
Since I can’t tell her
in person, i’ll tell you.
i wish her
all the happiness in the world.
Josuke: So, funny thing
about that picture I gave you.
I decided to hang on to a piece.
Shining diamond!
Joseph: Eh?
Josuke: Oh, wow,
you shouldn’t have!
Though i’ll take it
if you insist!
We’ll just call this gift
16 years of back allowance!
Besides, think about what
your better half would say
if you took that picture
home with you!
joseph: Who does
that cocky punk think he is?
Jotaro: I’m starting to see
that golden spirit, old man,
and he’s seeing it
all the way to the bank.
Josuke: You take
good care of yourself!
( Joseph growls )
( Chuckles )
- ( Jotaro chuckles )
- ( Baby coos )
Koichi: The invisible baby’s
mother was never found,
so Joseph joestar
Rose to the occasion
and began an adventure
as a new dad.
Jotaro kujo finally finished
a doctoral thesis he began
on a species of starfish
he found on a beach in morioh,
earning him his phd.
( Tomoko groans )
Damn that josuke!
He’s always coming in here
and eating all my food
like he owns the place!
( Groans )
I’ll just drink his juice!
Yukako: Koichi!
- koichi: Huh?
- Yukako: Sorry i’m late!
I was making bento boxes for us
and lost track of the time.
Koichi: Wow, you actually
made us a special lunch?
That’s so thoughtful!
Lunchtime can’t come
soon enough. ( Laughs )
Singers: ♪ bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ Great days
- ♪ breakdown...
Okuyasu: Tasty!
( Sighs )
( Squeals happily )
Now we’re cookin’!
Let the healing begin!
Don’t fight it!
Let the food cure you!
If this works, you’ll be
a normal old dad again!
Isn’t that great?
( Mr. Nijimura sighs )
( Okuyasu groans )
Well, that didn’t work!
- ( Chuckles )
- ( Stray cat meows )
Akemi: My skin is so smooth!
Yoshie: Check out
my refreshed eyes!
Reiko: The food here
is out of this world!
Yuya: Isn’t it, though?
Thanks to this food,
i’m even
more stunningly gorgeous now.
What am I gonna do
with myself?
reiko:
You’re simply radiant, yu.
akemi: Yeah,
you’re practically beaming!
Yuya: Mm. You think so?
Would you say i’m a dazzling
dish of devilish delights?
- ( All laughing )
- Tonio: Grazie!
Well, amico mio,
until next we meet.
Ayana: I just saw ko
holding hands with a girl,
and she was drop-dead gorgeous.
Mrs. Hirose: Oh, my!
Are you sure?
He never mentioned anything
to me about a girlfriend.
Woman: Did you hear?
Mr. Kira went missing.
Woman 2: Yeah, I did!
They’re saying they found him
dead without a face.
Woman 1: How freaky.
Hazamada: And just how are you
gonna make this up to me?!
Tomami: Say what?!
hazamada:
That stupid can you kicked
sprayed juice all over
my brand-new manga,
so I wanna know what you’re
gonna do to make this right?
Tamami: Jeez, kid,
cry me a river!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
All right, let’s get started.
( Yelling )
singers:
♪ breakdown, breakdown...
Kanedaichi: You sure
spend a lot of time
staring out into the distance.
You see anything cool?
I just see plain old morioh.
Mikitaka: Exactly.
Isn’t it grand?
I find this town interesting,
quite interesting indeed.
Koichi: And so, for most,
the summer of 1999
slipped away like any other.
Peace had come to morioh,
making for
some pretty great days.
singers:
♪ give you an answer...
- Okuyasu: Hey, did you hear?
- Josuke: Hmm?
Apparently, Rohan got caught
shoplifting from kame yu.
- What a dipshit.
- Okuyasu: Huh?!
josuke: Man, that’s
freakin’ crazy, if it’s true.
okuyasu:
What do you mean by "if"?
I mean, it has to be, right?
koichi: Wait.
You don’t know for sure?
( Josuke sighs ) Dumb-ass.
Well, come on. Let’s bounce.
- Singers: ♪ great days
- ♪ breakdown, breakdown
♪ breakdown, breakdown