singers: ♪ mori, mori, mori, mori
♪ morioh Cho radio
announcer: We’re live. Morioh Cho.
Kai: You’re listening to morioh radio.
Kai harada here, keeping you company on this fine day.
- Remember last week’s topic? - Koichi: Wow!
Just look at those spokes sparkle and spin!
i can’t believe I got this mountain bike
as a graduation gift.
Getting new stuff is always such a blast.
And with a bike this amazing,
i’ll never ride the school bus again!
- ( Yelps ) - ( Squish )
( Grunting )
( Groans )
( Wheels clacking )
( Groans ) That hurt.
Huh? What happened?
And what’s that bag doing there?
( Cat meowing )
No, it can’t be.
You mean that bag had a...
( Yells ) Oh, my god! I ran over a cat!
But how?! I didn’t even see it lying there!
There was no way I could have dodged the poor thing in time!
- Man: Exactly right! - Koichi: Huh?
man: That was just a bit of bad luck.
it’s not like you meant to run it over.
Nah, if you want my take on the matter,
the real scoundrel here is the ass-wipe
who left that poor kitten in a bag to die.
Pretty rotten, if you ask me.
( Koichi gasps ) We’ve gotta do something.
Man: What’d be the point?
You don’t hear the little fur ball meowing, do you?
It’s dead.
So what’s your name, kid?
I’m tamami kobayashi, and I just happen to have graduated
from the same school you’re attending. Huh?
Nice bike you got there.
So are you a freshman?
Koichi: Yes, I am. My name is koichi hirose.
Tamami: Ah, high school.
Boy, that sure takes me back. Good times.
At any rate, have a seat over here, Mr. Hirose.
Koichi: Uh, b-but I...
( Shudders )
Tamami: Come on, kid.
Quit that punk-ass quivering, and sit down.
Now that you’re nice and comfy, I have a proposition for you.
I’ll lay that pussycat to rest,
and you grease my palm with some cash. Sound fair?
Hey! There something wrong with your ears?!
Koichi: What are you talking about?
Tamami: Try to keep up. This is serious business.
I know you’re innocent and all,
but you’re not planning to pull a hit and run
with my precious cat, are you?
( Koichi gasps ) You’re saying that cat belonged to you?
Tamami: That’s exactly what i’m saying.
Koichi: Then, aren’t you the one who stuffed the kitten
inside a bag and left it in the street?
tamami: Let’s not get bogged down in details.
I’m asking if you think
you’re gonna walk away from this scot-free.
After all, the killer here...
Is you, short stuff.
♪
Tamami: I bet you’re feeling pretty guilty right now,
but the good news is paying a little fee
could just free yourself of that oppressive feeling of guilt.
so why don’t we begin the healing
by emptying out your wallet?
- ( Koichi gasps ) - Tamami: Well?
( Koichi gasps ) What is this thing?!
it looks like some kind of freaky padlock,
and it’s really heavy!
Tamami: Huh? You’re saying you can actually see it?
Hah! What do you know!
That’ll make things go by a whole lot faster.
Koichi: Wait. You mean this thing is a stand?
Why is a psycho’s stand growing out of my body?!
Okuyasu: Huh?
hey, josuke, you seeing what i’m seeing?
It looks like koichi’s down there.
josuke: Yeah, that’s koichi all right.
No doubt about it. No matter where he goes,
he always seems to end up with the wrong crowd.
( Okuyasu chuckles ) I’m sure he can handle himself.
Tamami: Four months ago, i crossed paths
with a guy by the name of keicho nijimura,
and he gave me a pretty handy special ability.
I hadn’t a clue what was happening, but it felt great,
and I figured if I put my new powers to good use,
i’d never have to worry about a thing
for the rest of my life.
All right, cough it up already.
Being cheap means the lock stays right where it is,
and you wouldn’t want that, would you?
koichi: I can’t help you, really.
I’m flat broke.
Tamami: Ah.
then explain why you just looked away.
Koichi: I didn’t. I mean...
Yaah! It got heavier!
Oh, no, i’m gonna...
( Grunts )
Tamami: Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Didn’t anybody ever teach you that it’s bad to lie?
Admit it or not, you know in your heart that i’m right,
and the guiltier you feel,
the bigger and heavier that lock will grow.
The lock’s size is proportional to the weight of your guilt,
and the two are inexorably linked.
you can knock me out or run a thousand miles away,
but you’re never getting rid of that thing.
So why don’t you be a good boy
and give me your wallet? how ’bout it?
Didn’t you say something about being flat broke, kiddo?
This looks like 7,000 yen to me.
Koichi: No, you can’t! That’s the money I was going to use
to buy new sneakers for gym class today!
Tamami: What? Sneakers?
You can go barefoot!
Josuke: Hey, man. What’s going on?
- Tamami: Huh? - ( Koichi gasps )
J-josuke and okuyasu, you’re here!
Josuke: Looks like a grown man’s mugging a high school kid.
Why don’t you get a job and earn your own money?
Tamami: Oh, butt out! It’s none of your business, so run along.
josuke: Sorry. That’s not gonna happen,
not when there’s a stinkin’ shit bag
and his dirty little stand in front of me.
I think it’s time to take out the trash.
Tamami: Hey, now!
Okuyasu: Damn thing won’t come off.
What kind of stand is this?
Tamami: Hold on a sec. You guys can see it, too?
How many of you freak shows are there?
Josuke: You took the words right out of my mouth,
but the answer to that question can wait.
’til then, i’d appreciate it if you’d remove that lock.
( Tamami growls ) Hey, you assholes,
don’t you underestimate me!
Watch yourselves, ’cause i’m not fooling around here.
It’s essential that criminals pay for their crimes
in order to keep society from crumbling around us.
If he’s not gonna pay,
does that mean one of you will cover what he owes me?
If so, i’ll let you go. ( Laughs )
Money’s money, after all.
Okuyasu: Oh, so you just wanna get your hands on our money.
I’d like to see you try.
Koichi: Keep your guard up!
This loser already swiped 7,000 yen from me!
Tamami: That’s because you lied straight to my face,
- you dolt! - ( Koichi groans )
Tamami: You really think that poor kitty’s life
is only worth a measly 7,000 yen?
Well, think again.
- ( Cash register dings ) - You owe me 500 grand, kiddo!
Koichi: 500 grand?!
Tamami: You bet your ass.
500--( Groans )
Okuyasu: Would you please shut your hole?!
Koichi: You did it, okuyasu!
Josuke: Yeah, but easy, man.
okuyasu: I’ve had it with your bullshit, you bastard!
You’re giving the runt his 7,000 yen back right now!
Are we clear?!
( Tamami groaning )
♪
- Okuyasu: Huh? - ( Tamami grunts )
( Koichi gasps )
( Tamami wails ) My front tooth! Gaah!
Okuyasu: Jeez, why the hell did you stumble around
like a drunk baby and make yourself fall over?
Tamami: Make myself fall?
You’re so mean!
how could you say such a thing after hitting me?!
Gah! My poor front tooth has been knocked out.
That’s--that’s cruel.
Okuyasu: Hey, wait a second. You are okay, right?
Koichi: No, stop, okuyasu. It’s a trap!
Whatever you do, don’t let him make you feel guilty!
( Okuyasu groans )
Koichi: He guilted you on purpose.
- ( Tamami wails ) - ( Cash register dings )
A front tooth’ll cost me a pretty penny,
and I don’t have any insurance. ( Laughs )
Okuyasu: Damn! You little--
tamami: Uh-oh! I wouldn’t do that if I were you.
if someone under my lock’s control
tries to hurt me in any way,
the damage will bounce back and hurt my opponent instead.
Okuyasu: Shit. You bastard.
( Tamami laughs )
Josuke: Hey, about that kitten you said koichi ran over...
- ( Toy meows ) - Would this happen to be it?
( Meow stops )
( Tamami gasps )
okuyasu: That’s a stuffed animal.
josuke: Now, getting down to business,
i’ve got your tooth right here.
( Shining diamond whooshes )
It’s as good as new.
Tamami: Huh?
- Okuyasu: It’s gone! - Tamami: Yeah, I know!
and I feel a million times lighter now.
tamami: J-just who the hell are you?!
Josuke: Hey, did you forget about the 7,000 you stole?
( Tamami gasps ) You win! Here’s the money!
Okuyasu: Now hit the road before we kick your smarmy, little ass!
( Tamami yells )
( Koichi sighs ) Oh, thank goodness.
- Josuke: Hmm? - Okuyasu: Huh?
Koichi: He took the bills and only left the corners behind!
he grabbed more than enough bills
to exchange them at the bank!
Josuke: What a douche bag.
( Okuyasu growls ) he’ll pay.
And it’s not even my money.
♪
Tamami: Damn. A measly 7,000 yen.
( Cash register dings )
but they haven’t gotten rid of me that easily.
I’ll get my revenge.
( Koichi sighs )
( Watch ticks, stops )
( Sighs )
That rotten morning practically ruined my entire day.
I’m glad it’s over.
I’m home, police.
You didn’t die, did you?
Woof, woof.
Hey, mom, i’m home from school.
Tamami: Truth be told,
i’ve heard quite a lot about you, ma’am.
- koichi: Huh? - Tamami: Beautiful, kind,
- and so refined. - ( Ms. Hirose laughs )
Oh, don’t be silly.
Tamami: No, it’s all true!
Ms. Hirose: Are you serious?
Tamami: Cross my heart, and hope to die.
Koichi: Wh-why is this guy in my house,
and why is he massaging my mom’s shoulders?!
Koichi: Hey, what is this?! And why are you here?!
Ms. Hirose: Hi, ko. Did you have a good day at school? Come in.
Koichi: I asked you a question! Don’t ignore me!
What are you doing here?!
ms. Hirose: Koichi, this gentleman was kind enough
to bring us the money you dropped on your way to school.
Koichi: Huh?!
ms. Hirose: 7,000 yen, young man.
Koichi: Hold on. This is unbelievable!
You told her you found it?!
Ms. Hirose: Well, of course.
After all, you did run into Mr. Kobayashi
on your bike today, didn’t you?
Koichi: What?!
Tamami: I just wanted to make sure
you got your money back, koichi.
koichi: Yeah, it’s the least you could do!
Ms. Hirose: I don’t understand. Why are you getting so upset?
Tamami: There’s another thing I should address, ma’am,
but it’s not easy for me to say.
It would seem as though i, too, dropped my wallet
when koichi mowed me down with his bike this morning.
funny enough, it looks just like this one.
I figure in all the confusion earlier,
mine was taken in place of his.
Do you understand what i’m getting at, ma’am? Think hard.
Ms. Hirose: Uh, well, that seems
like quite the coincidence, but I suppose it’s possible.
Tamami: Well, there you go.
If you would please tell koichi to return my wallet immediately.
It had about 500,000 yen, give or take,
and I would like to be paid back in full.
ms. Hirose: Oh, good heavens! How much?!
Koichi: 500,000?!
I get your game now, dirty con artist!
Ms. Hirose: Ko, what happened?
Koichi: You don’t have to worry, mom.
This guy is nothing but a fraud! He’s a liar!
Tamami: My, that’s so rude. I didn’t wanna bring it up,
but I have proof that your son swiped my wallet for his.
I decided to eat at jonny’s last night,
where I ordered the hamburger meal.
And, oh, that’s right.
i had a bowl of onion gratin soup on the side.
I believe it came out to 1,833 yen,
but I could be wrong.
the receipt in the wallet koichi has
should clear everything up.
( Koichi gasping )
♪
ms. Hirose: He was telling the truth.
Koichi: No, he’s not! You have to believe me!
It’s some kind of trick! You planted it, didn’t you?!
Then you went out and bought the same wallet to trick my mom!
( Tamami chuckles ) He has quite the imagination,
but his habit of lying and stealing
is a disturbing character flaw.
Somebody here raised a real delinquent.
As his mother, don’t you feel any guilt over his actions?
Koichi: That’s enough!
- ( Grunts ) - ( Tomoko chuckles )
( Koichi gasps )
Mom!
( Tamami laughs ) I was wondering when it would appear!
Now the weight of her guilt over her baby boy
turned criminal will oppress her soul.
I am gonna bleed you dry, kid.
First, i’ll take the house’s land, title, and seal.
Then we’ll see what else you got.
Ah, I have to give it to you. This is a great house.
- ( Laughs ) - ( Koichi shudders )
Girl: Koichi, is something wrong?
( Koichi shrieks ) Sis!
- Ahh! He got you, too?! - ( Tamami laughs )
That’s right, "ko." When your lovely sister brought me tea,
I got her to spill some on my hand.
I wailed to make her think she burned me,
and you should have seen how apologetic she was.
( Laughs ) So sweet and seductive.
and she’s a junior at an all-girls school. Yummy.
Fully grown and ripe for the picking.
( Laughs ) Ya-ya-yahoo!
- ( Laughs ) - ( Koichi growls )
Tamami: Huh? What the...
Koichi: Bastard.
mark my words. I’ll make you pay for this.
Tamami: Wait. What’s going on?
What’s that funny-looking egg thing supposed to be?
♪
tamami: Wait! What the hell is that?!
Koichi: Okay, you two, you need to leave the room right now!
Ms. Hirose: What’s going on, ko?
Koichi: I’ve got this, but you have to be quiet.
Tamami: I-I don’t know what that thing is,
but get it away from me!
You may have gotten your mom and sister out of the room,
but they’re still my hostages, and as long as they are,
you have to do what I say, so call off your beast!
( Koichi growls )
( Tamami wails )
Koichi: Hate to break it to you, buddy,
but you’re not getting anywhere near my mother or sister!
tamami: Fine. Do your worst then, koichi.
You think you’re a badass...
Koichi: After you take the locks off my family!
tamami: You’re a smart boy, koichi.
think about what it would do to your mother
if she saw you beating the shit out of me!
Her guilt would be all-consuming and swallow her up!
Koichi: I told you to remove the locks now!
Tamami: Who do you think you’re talkin’ to,
you sawed-off little dickhead?! I’m tamami kobayashi!
I’m not takin’ off the locks until i’m good and ready!
( Wails )
Huh?
that punch, it didn’t hurt at all.
( Koichi gasps )
hey, now. What the hell was that?
your friend’s bark is a lot worse than his bite.
What kind of stand is that, anyway?
As far as I can see,
it’s just a poser without any speed or power.
How dare you scare me over nothing?! Screw you!
It’s time I taught you a lesson.
a stand can have all the potential in the world,
but it means nothing without mental fortitude.
The hard truth is your feeble spirit
is weakening your stand!
but that just makes my payback so much sweeter!
koichi: T-there’s something weird on his cheek.
"Ba" and "gi"?
they’re like comic book sound effects.
( Tamami yelps )
( Ringing )
Tamami: What is this?
w-where the hell is this ringing coming from?
It’s like the sound I heard when he hit me before! Gaah!
Wait? What?
Why is there writing on my arm?!
Damn it. It’s stuck! It won’t come off!
( Whacking )
( Ringing )
( Wails )
No! This can’t be happening!
It’s like the blasted sound is coming from inside my body!
How can your stand have this kind of power?!
you little shit! Stop this damn noise right now!
( Gasps )
- ( Booming ) - ( Screaming )
Koichi: So that’s it. My stand has the ability
to fill the body with sound and turn it into a weapon.
Oh, now that I think about it,
we studied a famous matsuo basho poem just like this in school,
something about the trill of the locust
permeating through stone.
( Drop echoes )
Tamami: Damn! How’d I let this thumb sucker get me?!
Koichi: All you have to do is take the locks
off my mom and sister, and the noise will stop!
you can try resisting if you want to, but who knows
what effect the strain will end up having on your body?!
( Tamami growls ) Knock off the ringing!
- ( Crackling ) - ( Yelling )
Koichi: Stop trying to be a tough guy,
and take the locks off my family!
Tamami: Damn you! A pitiful bug like you
has no right to act so high and mighty!
( Groans ) The reason i’m such a boss-ass con man
is because I don’t cave in to upstart pissants!
I’m tamami, and the "tama" stands for "balls,"
so you’re about to see how big mine are!
( Koichi gasps )
( Growls )
I’m not scared of that knife or your tiny balls!
Tamami: Keep underestimating me.
I’ll show you a whole new world of horror and pain.
Here comes the agony of the padlock!
( Groans )
Koichi: What?!
( Tamami screams )
Oh, my god, no!
Not only is the cut shallow, but the pain and panic is fake.
- toss. - Koichi: "Toss"?
Ms. Hirose: Who’s screaming?
Sister: What’s going on in here?
( Both gasp )
Sister: Ko?!
Koichi: No! You’ve got it wrong!
( Both scream )
koichi: Shit! The locks got bigger!
Tamami: Yes! ( Laughs )
( Ms. Hirose gasps ) Ko!
why, son? How could you do this?
Where did I go wrong?
Koichi: Don’t believe it. please, mom!
You have to know I didn’t do this.
Sis!
Tamami: I’m the winner.
Told you you couldn’t beat me.
Now, hurry up, and get rid of this racket, koichi,
or your mom’s gonna die.
Don’t just stand there! Do you want the guilt
to crush your mom into a pancake?!
although, when a person is wracked with this much guilt,
death seems like a sweet release.
Ms. Hirose: That’s it. I can’t take it.
- it’s over. - Koichi: Mom, don’t!
Ms. Hirose: No more! I can’t live like this!
tamami: Your turn to stop being a tough guy!
Nix the sound, or you’re gonna watch your mom
paint the room with her blood!
Koichi: Actually, I don’t think I will.
Here’s a better idea. I’ll make it worse!
Believe me!
( Reverb yells )
Tamami: What?!
( Ms. Hirose gasps )
Koichi: Mom, i’m telling the truth. Believe me.
- ( Ms. Hirose gasping ) - ( Koichi echoing ) Believe!
Please, mom.
( Echoing ) Believe. Believe. Believe. Believe...
Tamami: She’s too far gone. She’ll never believe you.
- ( Ms. Hirose gasps ) - Koichi: Come on.
Ms. Hirose: Koichi. If his own mother
won’t believe him, then who will?
I have to have faith in my darling boy.
He’s always been such a perfect angel.
He’d never hurt a soul,
and I know in my heart he’d never steal.
Koichi: Yes!
Tamami: This isn’t good.
- ( Ms. Hirose gasps ) - koichi: Mom!
Tamami: It’s not possible.
Parents never trust their brats!
At least, mine never trusted me, so what makes him special?
- ( Koichi growling ) - Tamami: Shit!
( Gasps )
( Wails )
I was only joking! Please, ko!
Surely you wouldn’t kill a guy over a joke, would you?!
Koichi: Take the lock off my sister, too.
Tamami: I’ve already taken care of it.
I could never do anything to harm such a picturesque face.
And so you know, I was only kidding about taking your house.
I even gave you back all of your yen.
See? Joke!
Please have mercy on me!
I’ll do anything, master koichi!
koichi: Really? You’ll do anything I want?
Tamami: Yes! Just name it! I’ll be your personal underling!
Koichi: All right, works for me.
Your first duty is to bring me 500 grand by tomorrow.
( Tamami gasps )
( Koichi chuckles )
Take it easy.
Can’t you recognize a joke when you hear one?
( Laughs )
Tamami: That didn’t sound like a joke to me.
( Sobs )
( Reverb shrieks )
Josuke: Uh, hey, okuyasu,
is it just me, or is that guy really creepy?
tamami: Master, allow me to carry your bag.
Koichi: Are you sure you wanna do that?
Tamami: Oh, of course I do. ( Laughs )
master koichi, you’re a true man among men.
Koichi: Aw, shucks. You don’t have to butter me up...
Josuke: I swear it’s like we’re in the twilight zone.
Okuyasu: I don’t know what that means,
but my brain hurts just watching all this weirdness.
♪
♪ Anytime I need to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes, and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight, and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in, and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, i’d die to find out ♪