Shinobu: Hello.
Kawajiri residence.
Huh? No, you have
the wrong number.
( Kira laughs )
Superb work, hayato.
You’ve kept
that meddlesome Rohan at bay.
I dare say you’re a chip
right off the old block.
Shinobu: Like I said, you’ve got
the wrong number. Goodbye.
- Kira: I’m proud of you, boy.
- Shinobu: Happens all the time.
Kira: Now I have
even more reason
to provide
for my beautiful family.
But, first,
the adults need to talk.
( Hayato shudders )
Kira: Honeybunch,
i’d love a goodbye kiss
before I leave.
Shinobu: Huh?
- ( Sighs )
- ( Kira chuckles )
( Hayato gasping )
- ( Porcelain shatters )
- ( Both gasp )
( Shinobu shrieks )
What are you doing, hayato?!
That’s my expensive China!
Why would you do that?
What’s wrong with you?!
I never know what’s going on
inside that head of yours!
You act like you don’t hear me,
and I don’t know why!
- ( Hayato gasps )
- Shinobu: Where did I go wrong?
( Sobs )
♪
Hayato: You can’t
see it yet, mom,
but he’s a murderous psycho.
If I tell anyone about him,
the listener will explode,
and time will reset
to this morning.
It may not happen for a while,
but if we keep letting him
have free rein over our lives,
eventually he’ll kill us.
( Grunts )
♪
But luckily for me,
I now know about someone else
who has special powers
like Kira, Rohan kishibe!
I have to find a way
to talk to him somehow!
I have to get him to help me,
or we don’t stand a ghost
of a chance of defeating Kira!
Rohan: Hmm.
Hayato: Rohan’s already here.
If I approach him directly,
he’ll get blown to smithereens.
Then i’ll be forced
to relive the same morning.
I’ve gotta tell Rohan the info
without meeting him
face to face.
It’s time to change fate.
( Gasps )
What? What? My face!
What’s going on?!
Hang on! Rohan did this to me
when we met that other morning!
( Man sneezes )
Dammit.
( Women laugh )
Hayato: But i’ve
been keeping out of sight
this entire time!
There’s no way
Rohan could have seen me!
Kira: Once the wheels of fate
are set in motion,
there’s no turning them back...
Hayato.
♪
Singers:
♪ breakdown, breakdown
- ♪ listen up
- ♪ breakdown, breakdown
- ( trigger clicks )
- ( Tape rewinds )
♪
♪ Breakdown, breakdown
♪ breakdown, breakdown
♪ let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ Let the joy of love
give you an answer ♪
( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ Great days
- ♪ breakdown, breakdown
♪ breakdown, breakdown
( trigger clicks )
♪
Woman: Come on!
The weather report
never said
anything about rain!
Kira: I’m sure
you would like to believe
you shattered
your mother’s favorite teapot
of your own free will,
but you’d be wrong.
You simply experienced
a reoccurrence
of the pot breaking
from the previous morning.
It’s preordained, son.
That’s how fate works,
as you’re about to learn.
If Rohan transformed you
into a book the morning before,
then a book, you shall be.
That is what makes
deadly queen’s
bites the dust unstoppable.
It reverses time and nullifies
the exposure of my identity...
Which means
i’ll have the pleasure
of watching Rohan
explode into obsolescence
and still make it
to work on time.
Hayato: No,
I can’t let Rohan die!
I have to go save him
before it’s too late!
( Gasping )
♪
- ( Rohan groans )
- ( Hayato gasps )
Kira: Poor Rohan kishibe.
- ( Hayato crying )
- Kira: Now watch carefully.
The fool has absolutely no idea
why he’s about to breathe
his last. ( Chuckles )
But i’m sure he’s realized
that his life as a manga artist
has come to an end.
( Rohan gasping )
- ( Hayato gasps )
- Rohan: Koichi!
( Hayato sobs )
Reimi: Huh?
( Gasps )
♪
( Gasping )
No, not Rohan!
Oh, god, why?!
( Hayato shuddering )
Kira: Hayato,
your visit with Rohan
is now as if it never happened,
and the morning will go on
as it always would.
Of course, I could undo
bites the dust right now,
which means that rohan’s death
would become
a permanent temporal point,
but, for now, I think
i’ll let it do its thing.
I suspect a few of his cohorts
will be dropping by shortly.
When they do,
you’re going
to make me a proud papa
by exterminating
the lot of them.
You’re my own
personal land mine.
( Laughs ) But chin up.
As long as you’re
a good little secret weapon,
bites the dust won’t harm you.
So, relax, and do
whatever you schoolboys do.
( Chuckles )
Well, daddy’s
off to the station.
No slacking at school now.
( Hayato crying )
This is only happening,
because he
crossed paths with me.
It’s my fault! He met me
and got murdered for it!
( Gasps )
What now?
Isn’t there anything
I can do to stop this monster?
Koichi: Pardon me.
Can I ask you a question?
Would you happen
to have the time?
My stupid watch seems to be
out of commission.
Hello in there. Anyone home?
Hayato: Huh?
Yeah, it’s 8:33.
Koichi: You know,
I have this weird feeling
i’ve seen you before.
Now, where was it?
You wouldn’t happen to know
who I am, would you?
Hayato: No.
Koichi: Oh, well. My mistake.
I hope I didn’t
weird you out or anything,
but now I know it’s 8:33.
Thanks!
( Hayato gasps )
Koichi: Mr. Jotaro,
looks like it is after 8:30.
How strange. Rohan-sensei knew
we were coming. Where’d he go?
Hayato: These are
Rohan kishibe’s friends!
They planned to meet here!
Koichi: He left
the car door wide open...
Hayato: They must have
the same kind of powers as him,
so I bet they all came here
to question me
about yoshikage Kira.
Jotaro: Hmm.
( Grunts )
Hayato: No, no, no, no, no!
If they figure out
i’m hayato kawajiri
and start interrogating me
about dad,
it’s all over for them!
( Yelps )
Josuke: Sorry about that, kid.
I was looking for my friends,
and i’m still kinda groggy
from oversleeping.
Okuyasu: I know i’ve seen
this kid’s face before,
but, for the life of me,
I can’t remember where.
( Hayato gasps )
Koichi: Hey, look.
It’s josuke and okuyasu.
- Josuke: What’s up, bro?
- Okuyasu: Yo, koichi.
Hope your morning’s
been spiffy, jotaro.
Josuke: So we’re
still waiting...
Hayato: Th-there
are two more of them.
Kira told me that others
would eventually be showing up.
He was talking about them!
Josuke: ...Kid’s house
without Rohan helping us out?
Uh, sorry.
I nearly forgot I was
still hanging on to this.
I believe this is yours.
Hayato: Oh, thanks a lot.
Koichi: You know,
it might be the angle.
Oh, yeah, i’m sure of it.
I know i’ve seen
that face before.
I don’t know from where,
but he looks too familiar
to be a stranger.
Jotaro: Koichi, look
at the name on his backpack.
Koichi: Huh? Hayato kawajiri?!
Josuke and okuyasu: What?!
Hayato: Crap,
they figured me out!
( Hayato gasping )
Jotaro: Hayato kawajiri.
Okuyasu: What the hell
are you doing here?
- Josuke: Was all this planned?
- Koichi: Wait.
Could this have something
to do with Rohan-sensei?
( Hayato gasps )
What am I supposed to do now?
If these guys start questioning
me about my dad, it’s all over.
The bomb will kill
every one of them!
No, please don’t ask me
any questions.
If you guys
end up getting killed
who’s gonna get rid
of the murderer?
If I have to dupe them,
then so be it.
Whatever it takes,
I can’t let them die!
Jotaro: I’d like to ask you
about this photo.
To be more precise,
I want to know the reason
behind your video recording.
Be straight with me.
- Why were you--
- ( Hayato wails )
Shoot! Nosebleed! Oh, no!
I don’t know why my nose
started bleeding out of nowhere,
but I have to find a doctor!
- Sorry!
- Josuke: Hold it.
You said you got a nosebleed,
huh? Let’s see it.
Come on. Let me see.
( Hayato groans )
It’s bad. I need a doctor.
Josuke: Nah, I don’t think
it’s that bad.
- Hayato: Huh?
- Josuke: See?
- It’s not even bleeding.
- Hayato: Huh?
( Josuke chuckles )
Josuke higashikata.
Nice to meet you.
That’s jotaro kujo,
one of my relatives.
Derp-face over there
is okuyasu nijimura,
and that’s koichi hirose,
the nicest guy I know.
You go to budogaoka elementary,
so you’ve got some time
before class starts.
We won’t take up
much of your time.
- Now, about this picture...
- ( Hayato gasps )
Josuke: If it’s nothing,
we’ll just be on our way.
Hayato: It is something,
but I can’t answer
any of your questions!
Please don’t ask!
Josuke: You see
the man you’re filming?
Would he happen to be your--
hayato: I’m begging you!
Don’t say anything else!
( All gasp )
Hayato: Crap. What have I done?
Now they’re going to ask
even more questions.
Josuke: What do you mean,
"don’t say anything else"?
Hayato: They’re not gonna stop.
Jotaro: Just what is it
that we shouldn’t say?
Hayato:
There’s nothing I can do!
Koichi: Does all of this
have to do with your dad?
Hayato: The bomb’s gonna go off!
It’s gonna kill them all!
( Crying )
Koichi: What the hell’s
going on, huh?
Josuke: Why can’t
we say anything else?
Okuyasu: Yeah. I mean,
we haven’t even
asked him anything yet.
- Jotaro: Given his reaction...
- ( Hayato muttering )
Jotaro: It seems the mere act
of us questioning the kid
is what’s sending him
into a panic.
Koichi: That’s it.
I have no other choice.
If I die here,
they’ll still be able to live!
I’m the bomb, so I have to die!
With me out of the picture,
I know these guys
will figure out
a way to defeat that devil
and save mom!
- ( Gasps )
- ( Crunch )
Josuke: It shouldn’t
be this difficult.
Let’s just ask him
about kosaku kawajiri already.
Jotaro: Hold on, josuke.
Something is up with him.
Boys: Huh?
Jotaro: Hey, what’s wrong?
Hey!
( Hayato gasping )
( All gasp )
Hayato: No, I can’t do it!
Something’s keeping me
from slashing my throat!
- Jotaro: Wait! What?!
- Josuke: Isn’t that kira’s?!
Okuyasu: Yeah, it is!
That’s a face i’d never forget!
Koichi: It’s deadly queen!
( Star platinum yells )
Kira: Actually,
you’re looking at deadly queen’s
bomb type three, bites the dust.
To attack me now
would be futile.
In fact, the only reason
you can see me
is because i’ve already
entered your pupils.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Kira: It doesn’t matter
how many of you
have gathered together.
The moment you asked
about my true identity,
your fate was sealed!
( Trigger clicks )
( Hayato screaming )
( Screams )
Shinobu: Oh, hayato.
I guess you’re already awake.
I’m glad you finally decided
to answer me,
but there’s no need to scream
this early in the morning.
Breakfast is ready.
Come and get it.
( Door closes )
( Hayato crying )
I tried,
but I couldn’t stop him.
He got them, too.
It doesn’t matter what I do now.
In one hour,
fate will run its course,
and Rohan and his friends
will be wiped
off the face of the earth.
It’s over. It’s all my fault.
I can’t even kill myself.
If I died, he wouldn’t
be able to use his power,
but bites the dust
is programmed to protect me.
He’s unstoppable!
Yoshikage Kira is a monster!
Unless he dies
or decides to shut off
bites the dust
at just the right time,
those guys are
gonna be blown sky high.
He’s made sure of it.
( Sighs )
♪
He either has to die,
or shut off bites the dust
at just the right moment.
It’s crazy. I never
thought i’d ever be capable
of something like killing
a person in cold blood.
I mean, i’m a puny
11-year-old kid.
What could I do
against a monster like him?
A-a monster.
That’s it! 11 years old or not,
there’s one thing I can use
to take him down for good.
Kira called me
his secret weapon earlier.
Well, i’ve got my own weapon,
and it’s slumbering
in the shadows of the attic.
I’ve never prayed before,
but, if there’s a god out there,
I need you
to come through for me.
Please, god,
help me find the strength
to kill this homicidal maniac.
- ( Gasps )
- ( Feral cat meows )
( Hayato gasps )
- ( Feral cat growling )
- Hayato: So I was right.
The sun makes
this cat plant spring to life.
Then it attacks its target
by shooting bullets
of compressed air.
It’s incredible
it can generate so much power
with such little light. Awesome.
I’ll use its killer instinct
to send an air bullet
flying kira’s way
at point-blank range.
I have a plan, but when and how
should I execute it?
Mom’s here, so I can’t
do it inside or nearby.
Oh, yeah, my hat!
When I leave,
he’ll put it on my head.
That’ll be my chance.
He’ll come up right behind me,
right into point-blank range.
That’s when i’ll get him!
( Anchor coughs )
You’re kidding! Why didn’t
you say we were on the air?!
Good morning, all. It’s 7:55...
Hayato: I’m pretty sure dad said
he wanted
another cup of coffee.
Shinobu: Hmm?
( Telephone rings )
Hayato: Kawajiri residence.
No, wrong number.
This isn’t
the sakurai residence.
Shinobu: Sweetie, I have
something special for you.
- Come drink.
- ( Kira grumbles )
Shinobu: It’s a piping-hot
cup of fresh coffee.
Kira: Hmm.
Oh, what the hell?
It’s such a pleasant morning.
I suppose one more cup
before I leave for work
wouldn’t hurt anything.
Hayato: Everything
is set in stone
under bite the dust’s power,
right?
Once something is broken,
it’s destined to break again,
and there’s
not a damn thing I can do.
You said it yourself.
( Kira gasps )
( Shinobu wails )
Oh, no!
My favorite China tea set!
( Moans )
Hayato: Take that, ass!
All right, mom, see you later!
I’m off to school now!
( Chuckles )
- ( Kiss )
- ( Shinobu gasps )
Hayato: There’s nothing
to worry about.
I’ll never let anyone
hurt you, mom. Trust me.
( Kira growls )
Shinobu: Where did
that come from?
He’s always so aloof.
I never know
what’s going on in his head,
but then we have
mornings like this one,
and I can’t help but love him.
Let me. I’ll have this
cleaned up in a jiff.
No use crying
over spilled coffee,
but I hope it
didn’t burn you too badly.
Kira: It’s fine. Don’t worry.
♪
Hayato: He’s still not here.
( Women laugh )
Hayato: Where is he?
Why hasn’t he shown up yet?
Huh?
What’s going on?
He was already here last time!
What’s the holdup?
Woman: Come on!
The weather report
never said anything about rain.
Hayato: No. It’s already
beginning to rain!
I wonder if I
accidently changed destiny
by leaving the house
before he did.
No, that’s impossible.
If he’s gonna try and sneak up
to put the hat on my head,
there’s no question he’ll
try approaching me from behind.
Time is running out!
Lightning struck the Pepsi sign!
I’ve gotta calm down.
I’ve still got two minutes,
and I have more than two minutes
before Rohan kishibe
spontaneously explodes.
I just have to believe--
( gasping )
He’s hiding
in the shadow of the tree.
He’s been here all along.
How could I have missed that?
Kira: Under
any other circumstance,
i’d say this morning
was pleasant,
but hayato wasn’t himself.
Why, though?
I’m getting
a very strange feeling.
It feels like we’ve relived
this morning several times now,
maybe three--
no, wait. At least four times.
Hayato: Oh, no. Does he sense
that something’s not right?
It doesn’t matter.
There’s no time!
I have no other choice
but to blast him from here!
- ( Feral cat growling )
- ( Hayato gasps )
Could he have figured out
that i’m gonna use the cat plant
as a weapon to take him out?
Is that why he’s deciding
to keep his distance?
No way. If he knew,
he wouldn’t be that close.
Okay, i’m only gonna get
one shot to finish him off,
so I have to make it count.
If I miss, Rohan will explode,
his friends will be obliterated,
and that murderer
will deactivate bites the dust,
making
the whole thing permanent!
If that happens,
he ends up the Victor.
It’s now or never.
Just take
one more step to the left!
Hurry up, and step out from
the shadow of that shitty tree
so I can blow you
to kingdom come!
( Gasps ) What the hell?!
He hid himself even more!
Kira: The look
in hayato’s eyes this morning
radiated a tenacity
i’ve never seen in him.
It was almost
the exact same look those louts,
koichi hirose and josuke,
gave off.
I don’t know what it is,
but something’s telling me
I need to watch his every move.
Then again, as it stands,
hayato’s completely helpless.
Hayato: Shit, i’m screwed!
A few seconds past 8:29,
and the bomb will start
ripping Rohan kishibe apart!
Kira: Hmm.
What is this?
The brat is panic-stricken.
He’s like a desperate rat,
toiling and drowning
in a cesspool of filth.
I guess I was
imagining his tenacity.
Those are the eyes of defeat.
( Hayato gasps ) He came out!
Kira: You left home
without your hat,
so I thought
i’d bring it to you.
Hayato: If you’re listening
up there, thank you, god.
Thanks for working your magic
and making that murderer
leave the safety
of that tree’s shadow.
I’m ready to do this!
Now die, yoshikage Kira!
( Feral cat growls )
( Kira gasps )
What the--
( gags )
( Hayato gasps ) I did it!
♪
A clean shot. I did it!
Rohan: He still
hasn’t shown up yet.
Perhaps he took
a different route to school
and I missed him.
( Hayato growls )
Prepare to die, murderer!
Huh?
What the hell?!
Kira: You know, as of late...
Hayato: No way!
Kira: My nails have shown
unprecedented growth,
which got me thinking about
how lately my life has been
devoid of all that is good.
But the contents of this pocket
confirm my feeling
that a guardian angel
has returned to watch over me.
( Spits )
Remember when I broke
mom’s special teacup
this morning at breakfast?
The coffee spilled on my wrist,
giving me a nasty burn,
so I took off the watch
and placed it safe and sound
in my chest pocket.
And, lo and behold,
it was the right choice!
Had I not spilled
that fateful cup of coffee,
where would I be?
Hayato: How’s this possible?
Things were supposed
to work out this time.
No! I messed up again!
And in a few seconds,
everything’s gonna go to shit!