( Kira grunting )
♪
there’s nothing
yoshikage Kira despises more
than sticking out in a crowd
or being
the center of attention.
to think i’d suffer
such a sickening humiliation
in front of total strangers.
What’s going on?
Heart attack pilots itself.
How could it be ensnared?
( Grunting )
i have no idea
what’s causing this to happen,
but I have to reverse it
before it’s too late.
Man: How’s it goin’
down there, buddy?
Can we help you out?
you don’t look
like you’re doin’ so good.
Man #2: I can call your mama
for you if you want.
How ’bout it?
Kira: I’m just fine.
- Now beat it.
- Both: Eh?
Man #2: Yo, did you catch
what this dude said?
it looks like
he had too much booze,
and now the sloppy drunk
has forgotten
how to use his manners.
man #1: Yeah?
You enjoying the buzz?
Man #2: Nice suit you got there.
Me and my home-dog
just got fired,
and we’re flat broke.
The ladies ain’t exactly
lining up, either,
so when I see broskis like you,
I get agitated.
( Kira groans )
( Groaning )
( Man #1 laughs )
Don’t just lie there.
Man #2: Would you look at that?
Your shoelaces are untied.
Let me take care
of that for you.
( Man #1 laughs )
What a knot!
good luck gettin’
them suckers loose again!
( Laughing )
- ( Kira groans )
- Man #2: Huh?
( Chuckles )
Ah. ( Chuckles )
♪
( Gasping )
Man #1: Oh, shit balls!
What the hell did that?
Kira: It was a bomb
made by my stand’s power,
and that was deadly queen’s
bomb type one.
Man #2: W-what are
you doin’, you fool?
Kira: Today has been
a complete disaster.
All yoshikage Kira wanted to do
was live a simple, quiet life,
but those meddling maggots
just had to stick
their wretched noses
where they didn’t belong.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Boys panting )
Okuyasu: Hey, josuke,
what the hell happened
at that shoe shop?
I’m still kinda confused.
Josuke: Koichi couldn’t
really explain it
over the phone,
but it didn’t sound good.
let’s hurry! It’ll take
about five minutes to get there.
okuyasu:
You managed to crack it.
And if the bomb stand
took damage,
then its user just got
a nasty surprise, too.
Reverb: Please do not venture
too far from my side,
and so you’re aware,
my range is five meters.
( Koichi gasps )
reverb: I can see
this comes as a shock to you.
Make no mistake.
We’ve indeed matured.
our power is
much greater than before.
my inferior range
in comparison with act two
is an unavoidable shortcoming.
Moving outside
my five-meter range
removes the weight applied
to the target object.
If it does so, the target
will be excited to such a degree
that it will rush toward us
like an animal in heat.
Conversely, if your aim
is to pin the target down,
moving closer
will exponentially increase
the amount of force
applied to it.
So what’s it going to be?
Koichi: N-neither. For now,
I want him right there.
I just hope josuke gets here
before trouble shows up.
- Reverb: Eh?
- ( Koichi gasps )
( Kira panting )
( Koichi gasps )
♪
Kira: You know, I hear
a new gym is getting ready
to open
near budogaoka high school.
And given today’s events,
i’m now considering joining.
I should probably
build up my strength.
Then again, I haven’t had
the best luck lately.
I could end up
sharing weights with
or swimming in the same pool
as the dregs
who’d rather play
with their dicks than bathe.
( Groans )
it took me a total
of three minutes to get here.
( Chuckles ) I realized
the full extent of my weakness
as I tried to traverse
the crosswalk.
( Koichi gasps )
Kira: Question for you.
How many guests should I be
expecting to join this party?
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Kira: What?
You phoned someone
asking for help, right?
Josuke higashikata and
okuyasu nijimura are closest,
and being
about five minutes away,
i’d wager they have
two minutes to go.
you’re one
of their best friends,
- are you not?
- Koichi: Wait.
Kira: Yukako yamagishi
and that haughty woman
who runs
beauty institute cinderella
are stand users as well, right?
Though, I severely doubt
you’d turn to them for help
in your hour of need.
Koichi: Y-you’re the killer!
( Kira sighs )
In all the confusion,
I misplaced my other jacket.
no matter.
I’ll retrieve it later.
but first
I must do away with you.
( Koichi gasps ) I was right!
You’re the man we’re all after!
You’re the killer!
Year after year,
you’ve killed people.
I doubt you even
remember them all.
Reimi, shigechi...
( Screams )
Make him suffer, act three!
( Reverb yelling )
Kira: Deadly queen.
( Koichi groans )
That’s so not fair! Why does
this guy have two stands?
I thought a user
could only possess one.
Kira: While deadly queen
is my actual stand,
heart attack is a smart bomb,
which I launch
from the stand’s left hand.
that’s why
the damage i’ve received
has been contained
to my left hand.
( Koichi gasps )
Reverb: Before we proceed,
master koichi,
you should know
that you’ve just left
the parameters
of the five-meter range.
the force suppressing
his bomb stand will dissipate.
( Kira sighs )
Finally.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Reverb: S-h-i-t.
Since it has escaped,
I will have to initiate
three freeze again.
kira: How interesting.
Your stand’s range is limited.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Reverb: Which of them
shall be the target
of my attack,
the actual murderer or
that piece-of-shit bomb stand?
Unfortunately, master,
three freeze cannot weigh down
two targets at once.
koichi: Even if
we immobilize the user,
the bomb stand will just keep
charging at us on autopilot,
but if we stop the bomb,
the user
will rush in for the kill.
Reverb: Which will it be, sir?
I need your orders
before it’s too late!
( Koichi shuddering )
reverb: To whom
shall I direct my attack?
koichi: Fine!
Your target is the bomb!
Reverb: Three freeze!
( Gasps )
( Koichi groans )
Kira: Goodness,
a Valiant effort,
but it appears
you were destined for defeat,
no matter which of us
you decided to target.
I used to think heart attack was
my invincible Ace in the hole.
I never imagined it would be
rendered completely ineffective.
What a day.
I had to compensate a café,
and then I had a run-in
with some thugs.
Truthfully, I feel like
i’ve been taken for a ride.
This is a first for me.
never have I been
so challenged in such a way.
In fact, i’ve been left
with the slight taste of defeat
in my mouth.
Well, you’ve certainly earned
my deepest respects, boy.
You really are something else.
( Koichi groans )
kira: By the way,
you wouldn’t happen to have
any tissues on hand, would you?
A handkerchief would also do.
What is this? I’ve gone out of
my way to pay you my respects.
The least you could do
is converse with me.
Koichi: I don’t have any.
Kira: No worries.
Feel free to use mine.
quickly now.
Your nose is gushing blood.
i offered it
so you could clean yourself up.
I’m about to beat you
into a bloody puddle,
and in just over a minute,
your friends will arrive
to find nothing.
leaving you alive
just doesn’t sit right with me,
especially after the public
humiliation I endured.
( Koichi shrieks )
Kira: Oh, put a sock in it.
better yet,
why not take the whole foot?
This day has gifted me
with the exact same pain
you’re feeling now.
however,
I accepted it with grace,
as opposed to your tedious
whining, you mewling quim.
( Koichi gasps )
kira: Sit back,
and watch a real man work!
( Chuckles )
See? Tissues come in handy,
don’t they?
Here. Let me.
Blood or otherwise,
they say a stuffy nose
is a sure path
to slowed cognition.
If it’s any consolation,
not too long ago
I was groveling on the ground
just like you.
in one minute, I will
vaporize you with deadly queen.
Until then, why don’t
you learn from yours truly
and put up with the pain?
learn to be tough
in the face of resistance, huh?!
( Squelch )
( Scoffs )
( Groans )
- ( Koichi groans )
- Kira: Hmm?
Koichi: What do you know?
Your name is--
is yoshikage Kira.
( Kira gasps )
Koichi: You look surprised.
All I did was say
your name, Kira.
( Kira growls )
( Koichi groans )
Kira: You got a look
at my driver’s license.
But when did you have the chance
to pilfer my wallet?
You pathetic
little boot-licker.
Koichi: Don’t tell me
you’ve forgotten.
You reimbursed the café.
You couldn’t have given me
a better clue if i’d asked.
Kira: I don’t see
how the two are related.
Regardless, learning my name now
does you little good.
In a matter of moments,
you’ll cease to exist.
Koichi: Yeah, believe me,
I know all too well what’s
about to happen, but, even so,
if a pathetic boot-licker
like me
can figure out your name
that easily,
I guess you’re not as tough
as you seem to think you are.
Sure, you might get away
for the time being,
but you know what, Kira?
I bet your every thought
is mocking you
for letting a whiny brat unravel
the mystery of your name.
and if they aren’t,
i’ll do the honors for them.
A mewling little high schooler
just found you out!
You’re such a colossal dumb-ass!
I’ll be waiting for you
on the other side,
you murder-happy son of a bitch!
Kira: That’s enough!
That’s the end of that brat,
but damn him.
Why do I feel like I lost?
I let him provoke me,
but I still have a minute before
josuke and okuyasu show up.
I thought roughing the boy up
would settle
my turbulent spirit,
but I can’t say
I feel much better.
huh? Why would he
be wearing his socks inside-out?
I guess it doesn’t bother him.
( Groans )
♪
No. I can’t stand it.
( Both panting )
Josuke: That’s the wrong way!
Okuyasu: But the shoe store
is this way!
josuke: This path
will get us there faster!
- Okuyasu: Huh?
- Josuke: Hurry!
( Kira grumbling )
Put your damn socks on right.
( Sighs )
That gnawing unease is gone,
which means it’s time
to eradicate you
like the bug you are!
Deadly queen!
The tip of this finger
can transform
anything it touches into a bomb,
so for your execution,
I think i’ll have it transform
your student badge.
Bomb type one!
Jotaro: You did a good job
holding down the fort, koichi.
I’ll take it from here.
( Kira gasps )
What?!
( Blood spurting )
( Kira gasps )
This is a shock.
I didn’t think you’d be able
to prop yourself up
with those injuries.
You would have been better off
entering your eternal slumber
peacefully on the ground.
i’m fairly certain
I can see the trees behind you
through your gaping wounds.
- Jotaro: Nice watch.
- Kira: Huh?
jotaro: Go ahead,
and take one last look at it,
’cause i’m about to bust it up.
To be clear, by "it,"
I mean your face.
( Kira gasps )
you certainly are
an intriguing individual.
I would love to learn your name,
among other things,
but I really must mosey along
to my next destination.
I have a mere 20 seconds left.
Mindless small talk
just isn’t on the agenda.
( Jotaro gags )
( Gasping )
( Kira chuckles )
I have to be honest with you.
Your stand’s attack
was surprisingly feeble.
Stopping that pitiful punch was
like catching a little pop fly.
You’d have to be
an absolute neanderthal
to believe your feebleness
has any chance
of overcoming
deadly queen’s power.
Star platinum: Ora!
( Kira groans )
♪
what the hell?
How can you move so fast?
Jotaro: Good freakin’ grief.
I take it back.
Up close, that watch
is tacky as hell.
Although, to be fair,
i’d say that’s the least
of your worries now.
There’s something
that’s gonna look
a lot worse
than that piece of junk,
and that, my friend,
is your putrid face.
( Kira gasps )
( Star platinum yelling )
Kira: Wh-what is this stand?!
it’s so fast, it’s like
the damn thing has stopped time!
Star platinum: Ora!
( Kira screams )
( Trash cans rattle )
Joseph: Koichi, if you hadn’t
stepped up the way you did,
I would have been long dead.
Even all alone, you fought
valiantly right up to the end.
There’s no doubt about it.
You’ve matured.
You have my respect.
( Chuckles )
♪
( Josuke panting )
Hey, koichi! Koichi!
Okuyasu: Oh, no! Did we get here
too late? What happened?!
( Gasps )
josuke: Hey!
Koichi, jotaro, hang on!
Eyes open, okuyasu!
Okuyasu: Yeah, sure!
But what the hell?!
- How’d they get so messed up?!
- Josuke: Calm down.
We have to find out
if they’re still alive.
- ( Raspy breathing )
- Josuke: If they are,
I can heal them
with shining diamond.
( Kira groans )
Josuke: Yes! Jotaro’s alive,
but he’s barely
clinging to life.
Okuyasu: Koichi is, too,
but he’s not breathing!
You gotta hurry up
and heal him, josuke!
He’s not gonna make it
at this rate!
Kira: I can’t believe it.
Josuke and okuyasu are here.
( Groaning )
This is the worst day
i’ve ever lived through.
It’s been one disaster
after another.
( Groans )
Yoshikage Kira has always
been able to overcome
any obstacle
that’s gotten in his way,
and i’ll get out
of this mess as well.
( Groans ) I must.
Josuke: Where are you going?
Okuyasu: Look at him.
He got beat to shit.
Josuke: Listen. Turn around,
and don’t try anything funny.
You got it?
Okuyasu: What’s wrong?
Didn’t you hear what he said?
Show us your face.
( Kira gasping )
( Shrieks )
Be careful, you two!
You have to stay far away
from mukadeya shoes!
Another crazy explosion
might go off!
Get to safety! The first one
came out of nowhere
and blew the owner to pieces!
They were caught up in it, too!
( Wails )
Okuyasu: An explosion?
Josuke: Hey, just calm down.
Were you also in the blast?
Kira: I’m an office worker
who was nearby,
but now i’m going to die!
I’m losing way too much blood!
( Gasps ) Why me?!
Josuke: Hey, come on, man.
Calm down.
It’s gonna be all right.
I can heal you lickety-split.
All right, now tell me
where it hurts most.
Kira: My midsection.
I think one of my ribs
might have punctured my lung.
( Josuke groans )
( Kira gasps )
Please! Hurry and save me!
Josuke: Hurry, huh?
That’s weird.
Last time I checked,
i looked like I was just
an ordinary high school student,
yet you believed
I could treat your wounds.
( Both gasp )
josuke: I still
have trouble getting people
to let me in
to pachinko parlors,
but somehow I strike you
as a med-school graduate
ready and willing to fix
your little boo-boos? Huh?!
You totally took the bait,
which means you have the ability
to see my shining diamond.
Kira: Crap. I got too excited.
Josuke: That must make you
the killer we’re after,
and they are
your would-be victims.
( Kira stammers )
Okuyasu: Wait! Are you serious?
He’s the killer?!
Kira: It seems you’ve finally
hunted down your culprit.
You’re right. I’m the one
you’ve been looking for,
morioh’s resident killer.
You know my identity,
the true nature of my stand.
You even know my real name.
I suppose sleeping like a baby
isn’t really
in the cards for me,
but it’s just
a temporary setback.
Deadly queen!
♪
( Both gasp )
- Jotaro: Hmm?
- ( Koichi gasps )
josuke: The hell
do you think you’re doing?!
Kira: What does it look like?
I severed my hand.
It’s so excruciating,
it’s a wonder
i’m still conscious.
There’s so much blood.
Look at me. I’m a sobbing mess.
Victory and defeat
mean absolutely nothing
to me, kiddos.
I assure you i’ll survive.
i’ll live on
in peaceful tranquility.
It’s true i’ll have to live out
the rest my days
with the insatiable
desire to kill,
but make no mistake.
I’ll have my happy ending.
I hereby free you, heart attack.
You may act as you see fit.
Your final duty
is to protect me!
Josuke: You’re kidding me!
What is this toy gonna do?
jotaro: Josuke,
that’s a remote bomb stand
set to go
after thermal energy!
the thing is
completely indestructible!
If it hits you, your body
temperature will set it off!
( Shining diamond yelling )
Okuyasu: Shining diamond
can’t break the thing?
Josuke: Break it?
Why the hell would I do that
when I can fix it instead?
He was kind enough
to leave his hand behind.
All: Huh?
josuke: It’s not
the prettiest sight to look at,
but that hand is
leading us to our murderer.
Let’s go!
Okuyasu: Yeah!
Josuke: You’re not
getting away from us
that easily,
you freakin’ psycho!
( Kira’s coworker gasps )
Hey, you girls seeing this?
( Women gasping )
Kira: Mark my words.
I’ll do whatever it takes
to sleep peacefully again.
Coworker: Eh, Kira,
what happened?
Why is your face caked in blood?
kira: Hi, everyone.
Is it time to head home already?
( All scream )
Kira: Sorry, but i’m in a hurry.
See you around.
Koichi: The murderer’s name
is yoshikage Kira.
His address is morioh kotodai
1-128. He’s 33 years old.
Also, he wields a short-range
bomb stand called deadly queen!
Okuyasu: Just look at it go!
Where is this guy running to?
Josuke: It doesn’t matter
where he’s going!
When we find him, he’s dead!
He’s holed up in this building.
Okuyasu: Guys, wait a second.
Isn’t this...
Beauty institute cinderella?!
Josuke: Why the hell would he
come to a place like this?
Koichi: Uh, oh, no!
Dr. Aya!
Aya, are you in here?!
♪
( Boys gasp )
Koichi: D-Dr. Aya, she’s--
okuyasu: No way! It can’t be!
The hell did she do
to deserve this?!
Josuke: Look over there.
It’s yoshikage Kira.
He’s dead!
Koichi: Aya!
Josuke: This is awful.
Okuyasu: What the hell
could have happened in here?
♪
( Jotaro gasps ) Wait.
That man isn’t yoshikage Kira.
He’s got two hands.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Josuke: Huh?
Josuke: Holy shit!
His face is missing!
Koichi: What?!
okuyasu:
His fingerprints are, too.
That’s so weird.
Who is this guy?
Aya: He has the...Same height
and build a-as the murderer.
( All gasp )
Aya: That monster
brought him here
and murdered the poor man
right before my eyes.
He’s more ghastly
than I imagined.
He forced me to use cinderella
to replace his face,
as well as his hair
and fingerprints.
Josuke: Wait. Are you saying
he’s someone else now?
Aya: That’s right.
H-his new face--( Gasps )
Josuke: Shining diamond!
- Aya: His face...
- ( Jotaro gasps )
Jotaro: No, josuke,
don’t touch her!
Get back right now!
( Aya gasps ) His face...
( The hand yells )
( Aya screams )
♪
( Koichi gasps ) Aya!
Jotaro: He’s on the other side
of that door!
Josuke: He won’t escape!
- ( All gasp )
- Koichi: No!
You’re joking.
( Overlapping chatter )
( Okuyasu groans )
Everyone’s goin’ home.
- There are so many.
- Josuke: Damn it,
but which one is he?
Which one of these guys
is yoshikage Kira?!
( Koichi growls )
Yoshikage Kira,
you gutless prick!
Come out here, and face us!
Jotaro: So he managed
to slip away.
With his new face,
he’ll have no reason
to fear or hide.
you can bet your ass
he’ll stay right here in morioh
and go on living
just as he always has.