♪
Keicho: This arrow is irreplaceable.
There’s only one, you know.
It’s essential to my mission,
and losing it is not an option.
( Josuke gasps )
Hey, leave that arrow alone!
He’ll bleed out if you keep it up!
( Okuyasu gasps, groans )
Keicho: Because of the failings of my blockhead brother,
I now have no other choice but to kill you.
Nothing personal,
but I can’t let anything happen to the arrow.
It wouldn’t do for it to break
or catch the eye of some old crone.
Given my meticulous nature,
I feel somewhat compelled to return it to its proper place.
I mean, what should one do
when one is finished listening to a cd?
You should put the first in its case
before listening to the next.
That’s how everyone does it,
and it’s how I do things.
- ( Koichi gags ) - ( Josuke gasps )
Keicho: Now what’s this?
So you’ve decided to enter our abode?
Josuke: No shit, Sherlock!
How else was I supposed to beat your smarmy ass
and get koichi back to normal?!
( Keicho chuckles )
Okuyasu: Brother!
Don’t count me out just yet!
Wait for me to help before you attack him!
- josuke: Attack? - Okuyasu: I hope you’re ready!
this fight is just getting started!
Josuke: There’s something moving up there in the dark.
What the hell?!
( Okuyasu wails )
♪
Josuke: Okuyasu.
Keicho: Your stupidity is truly astounding.
If you hadn’t stumbled in here like a bumbling idiot,
worse company would have already destroyed josuke.
And what’s more, you walked right into the line of fire.
( Okuyasu groaning ) But, bro, I...
Keicho: Your stand, the hand, may be menacing,
but you, little brother, are a fool.
The incompetent will hinder the capable without fail.
I’ve told you over and over since we were kids.
And life is only worth living when it has growth.
You’ve heard that before, too.
Josuke: I’ve never seen wounds like those before.
What kind of attack leaves you looking like a pincushion?
One thing’s for sure. He’s hiding something.
Keicho: Poor little brother. You know, it’s idiots like you
who deserve to die like a miserable roach on its back!
He’s riddling the place with tiny holes.
What is he doing?
Shining diamond!
What kind of a monster attacks his own freakin’ brother?
( Groans )
Keicho: Josuke higashikata.
no matter how dire the situation,
he would never abandon this brat.
I’m willing to bet he’ll be back to save him soon enough.
He’ll die by my hand,
as will anyone who gets in the way
of this bow and arrow.
I’ll wipe them all out of existence!
( Josuke panting )
Now then, I think it’s way past time
you tell me about your brother’s stand.
( Okuyasu gasping )
Josuke: What kind of power does his stand have?
Spill it, and i’ll get rid of these holes in your face!
Okuyasu: Like i’d tell.
I’ll never rat my bro out.
Understand, fool?
Josuke: Have it your way.
I suppose that’s just how it’s gonna be!
Okuyasu: Eh? ( Gasps )
Josuke: All right, i’m going in.
Since you’re not gonna help, just stay outta my way, okuyasu.
Koichi doesn’t have much time, so I have to move quickly.
If earlier is any indication,
his stand’s gonna attack from somewhere in the dark.
One thing’s for sure.
This is gonna suck.
I have to rely on instinct.
Senses don’t fail me now.
Okuyasu: Where are you goin’?!
I gotta know, josuke.
Why the hell’d you heal my injuries?
Josuke: Be quiet. Let me focus.
okuyasu: Didn’t it cross your mind
that I might attack you? I am your enemy, after all!
Josuke: Are you serious?
okuyasu: That depends on how you answer my question.
Why the hell did you heal me?
I’m having a hard time piecing things together,
so hurry up, and tell me, damn it!
Also, what the hell happened to your hand?
Did my bro do that to you when you were pulling me out here?
none of this is making any sense.
Why’d you go through so much trouble to try and save me?
josuke: Well, it’s not complicated.
I didn’t think anyone needed to die today.
truth be told, it’s as simple as that.
( Okuyasu shuddering )
Josuke: Koichi.
♪
He was taken upstairs.
( Stairs creaking )
( Creaking continues )
Okuyasu: I’m not finished asking questions, josuke!
Josuke: Have you lost your goddamn mind?!
I’m trying to rescue koichi he--
okuyasu: I wanna know why!
why didn’t you use your stand’s healing power
to patch up those holes in your hand?!
instead of wrapping it like that,
you could just make it all better like you did my face!
Josuke: Unfortunately, that’s not how it works.
shining diamond can’t heal my own wounds.
The fact of the matter
is life isn’t always as easy as we want it to be.
While we’re on the subject,
I can’t bring back the dead, no matter how hard I try.
( Okuyasu gasps )
Josuke: Last thing, okuyasu.
I don’t know how koichi’s doing, but if he doesn’t pull through,
i’m gonna take it out on your brother.
So if shit hits the fan, be pissed off at your bro,
’cause all of this is his fault!
Understand me?
If so, go outside, and wait.
( Creaking resumes )
♪
( Koichi gasping )
Koichi!
Shit. This has to be a trap.
He’ll probably ambush me as soon as I get close to koichi.
But...
Even if it is a trap,
this may be my only chance to save him!
His life is on the line, so there’s no time to hesitate!
What?!
Damn, you bastard!
Okuyasu: Josuke!
Josuke: He teleported.
okuyasu: I’m not the smartest guy in the world,
and I think with my heart instead of my head.
I’ll repay you for what you did for me, just this once.
That’s where my gratitude ends. I’m not helping you out anymore,
but I won’t help my bro, either.
This is it.
( Stairs creaking )
( Sighs ) Well, that’s great to hear, okuyasu.
Koichi: Huh?
Josuke: Hey!
You held up pretty great back there, koichi.
I’m so thrilled to see you’re awake.
How many fingers do you see?
Koichi: Uh, five.
I remember my neck being slammed hard between the gates.
After that, I was--
w-where the heck are we?
Josuke: Sorry to have to tell you this, koichi,
but things haven’t gotten any better
while you were napping.
All I wanna do right now
is walk down those stairs and leave this place behind.
but something tells me okuyasu’s bro
won’t exactly comply with that.
- ( Rattling ) - ( Gasps )
Koichi: Huh?
( Rattling )
Josuke: There’s no mistaking it.
Something’s lurking up there, but it’s staying out of sight.
what the-- something ran across that beam.
Koichi: Josuke, what’s going on here?
josuke: Koichi, I know you just woke up
and none of this makes sense, but for now
I need you to keep quiet and stay close to me.
It was a hell of a lot creepier when I couldn’t see it.
Getting a look at it is actually a relief.
Looks like we’ve got a pesky runt on our hands.
As soon as that little shit shows himself,
i’ll blast him to kingdom come with shining diamond.
Then we’ll get the hell outta here as fast as we can.
There you are!
What?! There’s a ton of those things,
and they’re all in some kind of uniform.
- ( Winces ) - Koichi: What the--
josuke: Looks like we’re being ambushed
by a bunch of toy paratroopers.
this is the power of okuyasu’s brother’s stand?
( Winces ) Damn it!
Son of a--
( shining diamond growls )
Dora! Dora!
( Soldiers shouting )
Josuke: I got a few, but taking out two or three of ’em
isn’t gonna be enough.
They leave tiny wounds,
but the damage definitely packs a wallop.
If we don’t play this smart,
we’re gonna be in major trouble.
Keicho: Since my idiotic little brother
decided to meddle with my trap and save that brat,
my plan has gone off the rails somewhat.
But in the grand scheme, it’s of little consequence.
You’ll never escape this house
or the domination
of my perfectly synchronized stand,
worse company!
Josuke: So his stand is called worse company.
( Koichi gasping )
Hey, josuke, w-what’s going on?
Josuke: Ask me later. I know it’s crazy,
but I need you to stay back.
They’re up to something!
Soldier: All units, halt!
Ready! Aim!
Fire!
Left face!
Josuke: Head on, these little bastards
have the firepower to blow us to smithereens.
( Gasps )
Luckily, we’ve got windows.
i know we’re on the second floor,
but we’ve gotta break those windows
and jump to safety.
( Engines whirring )
So much for that idea.
That’s just great.
They’ve even got helicopters?
But how’s his stand taking the form
of U.S. army apache choppers?
Koichi: Watch your back! They’ve got a tank!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Josuke: You’re right. Those are definitely tanks.
Koichi, carefu--
wait! Do you wanna run that by me one more time?
Can you actually see the enemy,
the soldiers, tanks, helicopters, all of ’em?
Koichi: Mm-hmm.
I don’t understand what’s going on,
but I can see them.
Josuke: The arrow. Since it didn’t kill you,
it must have given you a stand.
keicho: Oh? So the shrimp has one as well.
Keicho: He’s finally got the power to use a stand.
This certainly is a surprise.
Josuke: It’s the man of the hour, okuyasu’s bro.
This is a pretty ballsy move,
showing off your stand like that!
( Shining diamond yells )
Keicho: You can think of my stand, worse company,
as a cast-iron defense.
It renders all attacks and intruders
incapable of penetrating its protective shield.
I know you’re itching to put me out of commission,
( Chuckles ) But sadly, it’s a pipe dream
that will never come to fruition,
as your shining diamond’s attacks
will never get anywhere close to me!
( Josuke sighs )
keicho: Hmm. Feast your eyes on this!
The perfect symmetry of my army’s formation
is simply stunning, isn’t it?
Soldier: All units, maintain battle formation!
At ease!
Keicho: There’s just nothing quite like
having everything beautifully in place,
though you did destroy
a few of my foot soldiers with your attack,
so my troop’s formation is irritatingly asymmetrical now.
Josuke: Hah! Well you did say you were meticulous,
but did you really need to come out of your hiding spot
to tell us all that?
Keicho: Now, what on earth would give you that idea?
I came out here to observe the little troublemaker.
Koichi: You mean me?
Keicho: Indeed, I do.
if I recall, koichi was your name.
Ironic that you appear to have the innate ability
to utilize a stand.
Manifest your stand right now,
and show me the extent of its power.
if today’s my lucky day, you may just possess the ability
i’ve spent so long trying to uncover.
( Josuke gasps )
Keicho: Show me your power,
and i’ll allow you to live.
( Koichi gasps ) But I don’t know--
josuke: And what ability would that be?
It’s about time you told us what your endgame is.
Keicho: I’ll be asking the questions around here!
Do I make myself clear, josuke?!
Keep in mind I still have you in my crosshairs.
You should be thanking me
for letting you live as long as I have.
Josuke: That’s just great.
Keicho: Let’s go! Get a move on!
Manifest your stand!
Koichi: What’s a stand?
Sorry. I have no clue what you mean!
keicho: Huh? It’s your first time?
Well, i’ll be! Very well.
Josuke, be a sport, and show him how to manifest his stand.
- josuke: What? - Keicho: The striking range
of your shining diamond is only a measly one meter.
It’s a long shot, but if this wimp’s stand
can compensate for the weakness of yours,
you might have a real chance at escaping my company.
- ( Laughs ) - Josuke: Good point.
A stand that could kick your ass
would be an awesome addition to the party.
( Koichi shuddering )
Josuke: Okay, materializing your stand is easy, koichi.
Ramp up the urge to protect yourself,
or maybe think about pummeling this guy
- until he’s black and blue. - Koichi: Huh?
Josuke: The rest boils down to instinct.
( Koichi gasping )
Josuke: A stand unique to your spiritual energy
- should reveal itself. - Koichi: Hold on! Say what?!
you can’t just spring that on me
and expect me to know what to do!
Keicho: You don’t know what to do?
Then please allow me to help you out.
Here’s some inspiration!
( Koichi wails )
Keicho: Do it, green beret!
( Koichi screaming )
( Screaming continues )
- Josuke: What?! - Keicho: That’s it.
( Koichi panting )
( Keicho gasps )
Josuke: Hey, koichi, you have to try moving it.
Koichi: What are you talking about?
Josuke: The stand! Now open your eyes!
Koichi: What stand? ( Gasps )
Are you saying I made this thing?!
josuke: Yeah, i’ll congratulate you later.
First we need to find out what this egg-shaped thing can do.
Koichi: What it can do? I don’t know what the heck
you think is supposed to happen,
but I don’t have any energy left!
That was the best I could do!
Josuke: You’re kidding. that’s it?!
- ( Shell cracks ) - ( Keicho grunts )
This stand...
enough! I’ve seen everything that I need to!
all units, get in battle formation!
Koichi, withdraw your stand,
if they destroy this egg, you’ll die, too!
Koichi: What do you mean?! I don’t know how to do that!
Keicho: Light ’em up, men!
( Shining diamond yells )
Dora!
Koichi: J-josuke!
keicho: Excellent. Those two have been separated.
The crack in that egg, the brat doesn’t realize it,
but he might have something there.
So the only man dying today is josuke.
Josuke: Word to the wise, sergeant bro,
if you’re trying to bring the roof of this dump
down on our heads in a fiery inferno,
then do it, and stop playing around!
( Keicho scoffs )
♪
Josuke: This is great. Yeah, i’m in the mood for a brawl.
Keicho: Josuke higashikata,
is it true that you strongly disapprove
of disparaging remarks related to your hair?
Josuke: Why don’t you find out for yourself?
Go on. I dare you.
Keicho: Thanks, but I don’t think that’ll be necessary.
Instead, i’ll blow your head right off
from underneath that prized hair of yours.
Consider yourself forewarned.
But first, worse company will fire bullets into your legs.
That’ll keep you from running away.
Next, we’ll focus on taking out your arms.
Once that’s done, you’ll have no means of defending yourself,
giving me carte blanche
to blow your brains and hair into oblivion!
Josuke: Well, that sounds like a bulletproof plan,
if I ever heard one,
if you overlook the fact that it’s completely impossible!
Keicho: I’ve already told you how meticulous I am.
When I declare something, I stick to it, thus the warning.
Koichi: He’s wide open.
All I have to do is make that stand thing appear again.
It’s only an egg, but if I can somehow
hurl it at him and make a direct hit,
I might be able to beat him.
all right, koichi. Time to rise to the occasion.
I’m gonna beat him!
Keicho: Remember the only reason
i’m still letting you draw breath
is because your stand intrigues me.
Josuke: Bastard!
Keicho: All units, aim! fire at will!
( Shining diamond yelling )
( Okuyasu growls )
Josuke: Hey, sergeant bro, have you ever heard the story
where Moses parts the waters of the red sea
right down the middle?
Because that’s what i’m about to do
to your pathetic army.
Then i’m gonna beat you down!
Keicho: My plan is proceeding exactly as I forewarned,
but you’re too big of a fool to see it, josuke higashikata!
( Click )
Josuke: A land mine?!
Keicho: First your legs will go.
now, apaches, release your firepower, and disable him!
Shining diamond: Dora!
( Josuke groans )
He got my arm.
( Keicho chuckles )
First the legs, then the arms,
exactly as I predicted.
Hellfire is going to rain down on you
with a flurry of bullets!
Can those wounded arms of yours save you,
or will worse company tear you apart?
Let’s find out as it fires every missile, shell, and round!
You lose, josuke higashikata!
All units...
Ready! Aim!
Hmm?
and what exactly do you think you’re doing?
could it be you’re accepting your fate?
( Laughs )
or is it that you’re asking me to show you mercy?
Hmph. Well, no can do.
All units, take him out!
you think you’ve got me cornered,
but i’ve already implemented my tactics.
Keicho: Eh?
What?!
I’m sure those are the missiles I shot at josuke’s arm.
He turned them against me!
♪
Josuke: What? Did you forget?
My shining diamond’s special ability
is to repair almost anything that’s been broken.
Really, if you’re that forgetful,
you might want to take some notes,
and make sure you’re meticulous.
♪
♪ Anytime I need to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes, and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight, and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in, and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, i’d die to find out ♪