- Man: Koichi.
- Koichi: Huh?
Eh? Huh?
Man: I’m over here, koichi.
( Koichi yelps )
R-Rohan kishibe!
Rohan: Now, now, you don’t
have to be so defensive.
My days of causing you harm
are long past.
besides, after reading
your history with heaven’s door,
I found myself filled with
a deep sense of respect for you.
I’d go so far as to say
we’re two peas in a pod.
Wouldn’t you agree? ( Chuckles )
( Koichi whimpers, chuckles )
Rohan: Now then, i’d like
to ask you a question if I may.
You see, I used to call
this area around here my home
until I was four or so.
I’ve spent the day trying
to find my old residence.
Nostalgia must have
gotten the better of me.
Recalling one’s childhood
is central
to a manga artist’s work.
However, those memories
belong to a four-year-old,
- so they’re a little bit foggy.
- Koichi: Oh.
Rohan: That’s why
I need your help.
my question
concerns this town map.
There’s something odd about it.
look. This is
the soba shop arisugawa,
kisara drugstore,
and the owson convenience store.
They’re situated right to left.
Koichi: Huh?
Rohan: Now take a look
at the shops themselves.
From the right,
you can see arisugawa,
kisara drugstore, and then...
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Rohan: You have owson
on the far left. See?
Koichi: Huh? That’s weird.
The map doesn’t show a road
between owson and the drugstore.
What sloppy work.
Rohan: Koichi,
would you tag along?
I would be forever in your debt
if you’d be my guide for a bit.
Koichi: Huh? Well, i’d like to,
but the thing is...
Rohan: That’s the response you
give after I ask so politely?
Fine. Have it your way.
I didn’t realize
showing me around
for a few meters
would be such a burden.
koichi: He sure
is self-centered. ( Sighs )
I can only spare five minutes.
Okay, sensei?
Rohan: Strange, isn’t it?
I’m checking my official
shoin press
ultra-detailed map of morioh,
and it makes no mention
of this street existing.
Koichi: On the bright side,
since your map had an error,
you might get a gift certificate
at the bookstore.
( Groans )
Rohan: Blast it.
This map is absolutely useless.
Take a look, koichi.
It doesn’t show the yonemori,
honma, or onadera residence.
There are mistakes everywhere.
The bookstore’s going to owe me
more than two or three
gift certificates.
Koichi: Rohan-sensei, this place
looks like it’s been abandoned.
What a weird area.
The few houses
that are around here
- look completely unoccupied.
- Rohan: And look.
Even the vending machines
are out of order. Hmm?
Koichi: What the--
it’s the mailbox.
We made our first turn
at this corner
when we came down the alleyway.
This is too weird.
Somehow we’ve managed to end up
right back where we started.
Rohan: But we turned right,
left, then right.
( Swallows )
keep your guard up.
There could be an enemy nearby
manipulating things
with their stand.
( Koichi gasps ) You think?
Rohan: If you would,
have reverb fly overhead
and search the area.
( Koichi gasps )
Yeah, of course.
from up there,
it can see where we need to go.
Reverb act one.
( Reverb gasps )
Rohan: What’s the matter?
Koichi: There was
something up there.
I don’t know what, but something
just grazed reverb.
Rohan: Are you sure?
I didn’t see anything.
Koichi: I know something
came into contact with reverb.
Girl: ’scuse me.
Are you two lost?
( Koichi gasps )
Girl: I would be happy
to be your guide.
Rohan: A girl.
Koichi: She must be
the enemy stand user.
- Rohan: Heaven’s door!
- ( Girl gasps )
Rohan: And with the flick
of a finger, victory is mine.
We should be safe now.
I’ve written commands
in her pages,
so she won’t be able to harm us.
Koichi: Sensei,
that was amazing.
It’s like you launched
your drawing into midair.
I’ve made quite a lot
of progress with my stand.
That said, it still doesn’t work
on haters like josuke,
who wouldn’t know art
if it kicked him in groin.
she and I are
on the same wavelength.
oh, dear. She’s just
an ordinary girl, not an enemy.
koichi: Huh?
So she’s not out to get us?
Rohan: That’s right.
You can’t conceal anything
from heaven’s door.
Her name is reimi sugimoto,
age 16.
her address
is 312 kotodai, morioh.
That’s not far from here.
She has no boyfriend,
and her measurements
are 82, 57,
and 84 centimeters.
There’s a mole
by her left nipple,
and her first period came
at age 11 in September.
The first time she kissed a boy,
he rammed his tongue
down her throat.
Koichi: That’s just
about enough, Rohan!
If this girl’s not a stand user,
then I refuse to allow you
to read anything else
about her life!
Rohan: All right, all right.
I get it.
take it easy.
"I will forget everything
that has just happened." There.
Reimi: I’d be happy
to guide you.
Really, this place
trips a lot of people up.
Several of these alleys
look the same.
Rohan: Please point us
in the right direction,
and we’ll be on our way.
Reimi: Absolutely not.
A simple explanation
won’t cut it.
I’m your guide, so follow me.
- Rohan: Hmm.
- Koichi: Huh?
- Reimi: Want one?
- Both: Mm-mmm.
Reimi: If you’re sure.
but you still
have to hold on to the end.
Rohan: Hmm?
Reimi: Uh-oh. Better be careful.
Some girl is gonna dump you.
Rohan: Really?
Where’s your proof?
Reimi: Pocky fortunetelling.
The break tells me
all about you.
You’re majorly self-centered,
and you have a habit of pushing
people’s buttons, don’t you?
that’s why
you’re going to get dumped.
Rohan: Get a load
of this, koichi.
now we know
she’s off her rocker.
She actually thinks
i’m self-centered.
You’re about to find out
two can play at this game.
Light pink nail Polish
means you’re afraid of love.
That’s very telling.
you often let love
slip through your fingers.
( Reimi gasps )
No way.
Rohan: I use psychological
prodding over fortunetelling.
But enough about your love life.
something else
is weighing on your mind.
♪
Hmm?
Reimi: Have you heard
the story about this house?
It’s said it was the scene
of a murder 15 years ago.
Koichi: Did she say a murder?
Rohan: Yes, she did.
Reimi: No one lives
in the house now.
It’s empty. Here’s why.
This story was told to me
by the old lady next door.
it happened
in the dead of night,
while the young girl was
sleeping soundly in her bedroom.
she awoke
to a strange dripping sound
that seemed to be emanating
from her parents’s room,
but she couldn’t be sure.
( Koichi swallows )
Reimi: The sound puzzled her.
"Daddy," "mommy,"
she called out,
but she never heard a reply.
however, the girl
wasn’t particularly scared,
because she was accompanied
by her trusty dog.
Rohan: Her dog?
reimi: Yes.
He was a big guard dog.
In the darkness, she’d offer
her hand to him under the bed,
and he’d always respond
with a whimper and a lick.
arnold was
her constant reassurance,
but the dripping
that had stolen the girl
from her peaceful slumber
continued for several minutes.
Finally, she’d had enough.
her curiosity
drove her to investigate.
Koichi: What happened next?
( Gulps )
Reimi: She found Arnold
with his throat slashed,
hanging from the coat rack
like an old pelt.
The dripping sound
was coming from him,
the sound
of his spilling blood.
( Both gasp )
Reimi: Suddenly,
she heard a voice
coming from under her bed.
"Your hand is so sweet
and tender, sweetheart.
"Whimper, whimper.
I’ve already murdered
your mommy and daddy."
And then he attacked the girl,
- killing her where she stood!
- ( Koichi screams )
Tell me that story was just
your way of joking around!
( Reimi laughs )
Sounded pretty real, didn’t it?
You babies. That’s for
the nail-Polish crack.
( Giggles )
( Both sigh )
Koichi: Jeez, my heart
can’t take stuff like that.
( Steady dripping )
( Rohan gasps )
♪
( Gasps ) That means...
Reimi: Yes, the young girl
in the story was yours truly.
arnold and I
only exist as ghosts.
( Both gasp )
Rohan: Th-they’re ghosts.
It all makes sense now.
Heaven’s door could only access
her living memories.
this has never
happened to me before.
Reimi: The two of you
have stumbled upon the area
where I met my end 15 years ago.
i guess we’re
on the same wavelength.
This place is the gateway
between the living
and the dead.
( Koichi screaming )
Rohan: Come on, koichi. Run!
Huh?
♪
Damn. We’re stuck.
Koichi, call reverb.
it can give us
directions from above.
Koichi: She must
have been the one
who made contact
with reverb earlier.
Rohan: Never mind that.
just do it!
koichi: Eh? What?
A wall appeared in the sky.
Rohan: No, that’s not it.
Reverb’s actually
touching the ground.
Koichi: Huh? What in the--
Rohan: I can’t believe this,
but you’re the one
who’s floating.
Reimi: There’s only one way
to truly escape.
Anything else is futile.
I’m the only one
who knows where it is.
Rohan: This doesn’t
make any sense.
how the hell
do we fight a ghost?
Koichi: Please, whatever you do,
don’t possess us.
Reimi: Hold on just a minute.
Quit treating me
like a vengeful spirit.
I haven’t done a single thing
to either of you,
but somehow
you’ve found a way
to scare yourselves
half to death.
Listen, I didn’t trap
you guys here.
we’re standing
between the living world
and the world of the dead.
Wait a second. You two hold
some kind of power, right?
and you said
they’re called stands?
Maybe that’s why you’re
mixed up in all this.
Rohan: So you’re really
not here to attack us?
reimi: You’re even
more suspicious than I thought.
i guess i’m proof
of that stone tape theory.
Once I became a ghost,
I was bound to this place.
I’ve been here 15 years.
In all that time, i’ve never
stopped pleading with people
to listen,
to let me share my story.
But you two are the first
who have truly listened.
i gave you my word
i’d help you get out of here,
so that’s what i’m going to do,
but after I finish the story.
Koichi: There’s more?
Reimi: Now, as I was saying,
the murderer,
before I got
a look at his face,
his knife
found its way into my back.
it was late and dark,
and I was doing my best to flee.
i died,
but my killer still lives.
He’s living his life
right here in morioh.
( Both gasp )
Reimi: That’s what
i’ve been aching to say.
Not only is he in town,
he’s blended in.
Rohan: Let’s back
this specter train up.
Why are you confessing
all this to us?
Reimi: Relax. I’m not
asking you to catch him.
i just need you
to tell someone who will.
You can tell the cops
or anybody else
you think is up to the task.
Rohan: Slow down.
Why the hell should
that kind of responsibility
fall on our shoulders?
- Koichi: Rohan-sensei!
- Rohan: Compose yourself.
I think it’s best
we remain levelheaded.
It’s an absolute tragedy.
I’m sorry your life
was stolen from you.
but that still
doesn’t explain things.
We find the murderer
so you can get closure?
That all seems rather pointless,
doesn’t it?
You’d be better off
letting go of this world.
Surely moving on
to the next world
would be a better existence
than haunting these alleyways.
Reimi: Tell me,
do you have any idea
how many innocent boys and girls
have gone missing
from this town?
Rohan: No.
Reimi: Then you should know
it’s eight times
the national average.
( Koichi gasps )
reimi: Yes,
and it gets even worse.
Some are being slaughtered
in silence.
And he’s behind it all.
Koichi: Wait a minute!
You can’t be serious!
This is still going on,
and no one’s done anything?!
Rohan: Hey! You can’t
just say things like that!
According to this story,
you didn’t even see his face.
How would you know
what’s going on?
Reimi: I know, because I see
the souls of his victims
dominating the skies!
It’s as clear as day!
The wounds of those souls
are the same as mine!
( Rohan gasps )
Koichi: It’s horrifying.
That gash is so deep.
Reimi: I can’t speak with those
traveling to the other side,
but I see them depart
over and over.
he’s fueled
by a twisted obsession,
one I know all too well.
Morioh has always been my home,
and for 15 years, it’s stood
in the shadow of murder.
It’s terrifying,
and on a personal level,
it’s utterly humiliating.
When they finally detain
that wild animal,
my cherished morioh
will have a new reputation.
All of Japan will know it
as the home of a monster.
But none of that
changes the fact
that we have to stop him
as fast as possible.
He’s preying on someone
as we speak,
and there’s nothing
at all I can do.
Whose life will be ripped away
from them next?
You still have blood
pumping through your veins.
If you won’t take back
morioh’s peace and dignity,
then tell me who will, and i’ll
ask for their help instead!
( Both gasp )
Reimi: I really hope you’ve
taken what i’ve said to heart.
I’ve nothing more to say.
( Koichi shudders )
Well, I heard you
loud and clear,
and i’m shocked
no one knows about this.
There has to be something
we can do here.
( Rohan chuckles )
How altruistic, koichi.
This smells like trouble.
Although, this vicious killer
could be a good source
of inspiration.
It all seems like it’d make
for some interesting manga.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- ( Reimi gasps )
Rohan: Can we get out
if we go this way?
Koichi: Don’t buy
the good-guy act.
It’s obvious that he
has ulterior motives.
And when it comes
to trustworthiness,
the guy’s shady at best.
( Rohan sighs )
Did you hear a word I just said?
Reimi: Then we’re agreed.
i’ll show you
how to get to the exit.
Koichi: Huh? The exit?
Where do we find it?!
Reimi: If you go
past the mailbox,
you’ll find it on the left.
- koichi: Yeah!
- Reimi: Hey, slow down!
trust me.
You don’t want to rush it.
There’s a rule
to making it through.
( Both stammer )
Rohan: There’s a rule?
Reimi: Yes. Once you
make it past the mailbox,
you’ll see the exit
about 20 meters away.
No matter what happens
around that corner,
I need you both to promise me
you’ll never look behind you.
Rohan: Why not?
What would be there?
Reimi: That’s just the rule
for passing to the next world.
Even Arnold understands
something as simple as that.
koichi: Okay.
If a dog can handle it,
I guess there’s no reason
I wouldn’t be able to.
Rohan: And if we do look back,
what happens then?
Reimi: Well, putting it
in layman’s terms,
your souls would be dragged
into the next world.
Put bluntly, you would die.
( Both gasp )
Reimi: But don’t worry.
It’ll be a piece of cake.
All you have to do is
look forward. Simple, right?
♪
( Rohan shudders )
Did you feel something, koichi?
koichi: Yeah.
When we passed the mailbox,
something flew past our legs
and went behind us.
Reimi: Remember, eyes front.
Just stay calm,
and you’ll be fine.
Koichi: You feel that,
rohan-sensei?
There’s some kind of ominous
presence creeping up behind us.
Rohan: Yes, i’m aware.
- ( Presence growls )
- ( Koichi gasps )
Something’s there.
I don’t know what,
but there’s something
right by my head.
Reimi: Just ignore it.
There will always be something
trying to make you look back.
I know it seems scary
and overwhelming,
but as long as you
don’t look back,
it can’t do anything
to cause you harm.
Koichi: There’s something warm
and runny oozing down my neck.
Ignoring this thing’s
gonna be a lot tougher
than you’re making it sound.
Reimi: Almost there.
Go through the light,
and you’re home free.
- Koichi: Huh?
- Rohan: What?
Koichi: But I can’t
take any more of this,
and it’s so far away.
Let’s run for it, Rohan-sensei!
Reimi: Panicking
will make it worse!
It’ll try to trip you!
( Koichi yelling )
Reimi: You’re safe now.
You made it.
You can turn around now.
go ahead.
( Koichi panting )
I’ve never been so terrified.
Thank goodness it’s ov--
reimi: No, that wasn’t me!
Don’t look back! It’s trying
to get you to turn around!
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Rohan: You idiot.
Reimi: Koichi, if only
you had waited for us.
But this didn’t happen when I
came through here by myself.
Why’d they trick him?
( Koichi screams )
- reimi: Koichi, no!
- Rohan: Huh. I don’t get it,
but if we don’t look,
we’re good to go, right?
You lucked out, koichi.
you’re with me.
Heaven’s door!
I’m taking your ability to see.
You’re welcome.
( Koichi gasping )
Rohan: You can
calm down, koichi.
I’ll reinscribe
your ability to see.
( Scribbling )
The alley between
the convenience store
and the drugstore,
it disappeared.
( Koichi sighs )
I’m just glad we’re back.
Reimi: I’m afraid
this is as far as we go.
( Both gasp )
Reimi: Well, at least
until he’s caught.
When that finally happens,
Arnold and I will look back,
and we’ll be reunited
with mom and dad.
Peace and dignity
must return to morioh.
only then
can we find eternal rest.
I’ll be right here if you ever
want to talk about anything.
You two don’t be
strangers, okay?
I’m here if you need me,
little Rohan, Mr. Koichi.
From the bottom of my heart,
I want to thank you
for listening to my story.
( Both sigh )
Rohan: She had some nerve.
Where does she get off
calling me "little Rohan"?
What an audacious ghost girl.
But, still, reimi sugimoto,
she has an unyielding spirit,
and that’s something
to be respected.
For 15 years, she’s waged
a fight for the living
with nothing but her courage
and trusted companion.
There it is. Reimi, age 16.
I never doubted her story,
but it’s nice to have evidence.
Monk: Ah, we have a visitor.
You wouldn’t happen to be
rohan kishibe,
the manga artist, would you?
Rohan: Uh, sorry.
Have we met before?
monk: Let’s see.
I’d say you would have been
about four when it happened.
It doesn’t surprise me
you have no recollection
of that night.
so i’ll start by saying
your house was close to theirs.
The night of the incident,
your parents
left home for the evening.
Apparently there was some urgent
business that needed attention.
Your parents and the sugimotos
were very close friends,
so they left you with them
while they handled
matters elsewhere.
( Rohan gasps )
Monk: Rohan, that night,
the one that claimed the lives
of the sugimoto family,
you were there
and the only one rescued.
Rohan: I was there?
Monk: You were able
to survive that nightmare,
but once you were
in police custody,
you started crying
and repeating this sentence,
"big sis reimi snuck me
out the window and saved me."
Reimi risked everything
to get you to safety
before the murderer
could find you.
♪
Rohan: Now it all makes sense.
no wonder
she acted so familiar.
And I learned something else.
My heaven’s door,
it can’t reveal
my distant memories
or personal fate.
Huh.
Narrator: If you
ever find yourself
wandering down this alleyway,
a word of warning.
You should never,
ever look back.
Koichi: I’m telling you,
I really met a ghost!
The girl you saw in that picture
is named reimi...
Josuke: Yeah, I get it.
i already said
that we believe you.
Right, okuyasu?
Koichi: She was also a student
at budogaoka high school.
Okuyasu: This cutie
is just my type.
If only i’d been born
15 years earlier.
Josuke: If she’s
gonna stick around,
we should probably meet
your ghost friend, too.
But fair warning, koichi.
if we go to jotaro
or Mr. Joseph about all this,
you can bet your ass they’ll
have one question for you.
"This unknown killer, is he
using a stand on his victims?"
Koichi: Uh, I guess
I really don’t know.
Josuke: Well, in that case,
it’s up to the police
and courts.
Koichi: What are you saying?!
There’s a bloodthirsty murderer
loose in morioh!
Josuke: Yeah, I know that,
and i’m telling you
that jotaro and
the speedwagon foundation
aren’t going after
an ordinary killer,
no matter how twisted he is.
Now take a deep breath.
He’s managed to avoid the police
for over a decade,
and they’re supposed
to be the best.
it’s not like
we’re gonna summon him
like waving down some taxi,
by force of will alone.
Let’s stay calm and take things
slowly and carefully.
So what did ol’ Rohan
have to say?
Koichi: He said the same thing
as you, josuke.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- ( Tires skid )
Josuke: Be careful, koichi!
You have to be alert
when you cross the road!
Koichi: I’m sorry
for the trouble.
♪
Man: Morioh used to be
a summer escape for samurai.
i know.
Such an out-there concept
might be hard to believe,
but my ancestors
were among them.
we were ruined
during my grandfather’s time.
All I have left is the house
that I currently live in.
Oh, and my miserable,
little office job. Hmm?
Hey, what happened to that nice
imported watch I bought you?
that’s right.
You left it in your bag.
How could I forget?
If I remember correctly,
it was loose on you.
We’ll fix that tomorrow.
Hmm? What’s wrong?
Why are you being coy
all of a sudden?
( Laughs )
Now watch your step
as you get out.
Let’s head inside.
A sublime weekend
is beyond those doors.
It’ll be our getaway.
♪
( Groans )
Look at this. You’re dripping.
Not at all becoming of a lady.
I expect you to clean this up.
( Joints cracking )
I can’t recall your name,
but in the long run,
does it matter?
And, brava. It’s all clean.
You should be proud of yourself.
Now, then...
I think we should make
some dinner.
What’s the best dish
in your repertoire?