( doorbell rings )
Rohan: IT’S OPEN. COME IN.
Koichi: ROHAN-SENSEI?
WHERE ARE YOU?
Rohan: OVER HERE, KOICHI.
( Koichi gasps )
ROHAN-SENSEI!
WHY ARE YOU IN THE CORNER?
WHEN YOU ASKED ME OVER HERE,
\h\h\h\hYOU DIDN’T SAY
YOU WERE IN PANIC MODE!
Rohan: PLEASE, KOICHI,
I NEED YOUR HELP.
I’M IN THE GRASP
OF AN ENEMY STAND.
Koichi: WHA?!
A STAND’S IN HERE?!
WHERE IS IT? WHAT’S IT DO?!
Rohan: IT’S OVER HERE.
DAMN THING ADHERED ITSELF
\h\h\h\hTO MY BACK.
Koichi: IT DID WHAT?! ( gasps )
( Rohan grunts )
Koichi: SO YOU’RE SAYING THERE’S
A STAND ATTACHED TO YOUR BACK?
\h\h\h\hRohan: THAT’S RIGHT.
IT’S A VERY SERIOUS DILEMMA,
AND I DON’T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
Koichi: CAN I SEE
WHAT WE’RE DEALING WITH?
- Rohan: NO WAY.
- Koichi: EH?
BUT IF YOU DON’T SHOW IT TO ME,
HOW AM I SUPP--
Rohan: IF I EXPOSE MY BACK,
\h\h\h\hIT’LL KILL ME
AND TAKE HOLD OF YOU!
\h\h\h\hCheap Trap:
NOW BURN THE PAGES, YES?
Rohan: HEAR THAT?
EVEN AS WE SPEAK,
- IT’S WHISPERING IN MY EAR.
- Koichi: HUH?
( Rohan stammers )
Koichi: YOU’RE NOT MAKING SENSE!
WAIT! THIS IS ALL SOME BIG JOKE
AT MY EXPENSE, ISN’T IT?
Rohan: HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT?!
\h\h\h\hI JUST TOLD YOU IF I
EXPOSE MY BACK, I’M DONE FOR!
Koichi: OH, I HEARD YOU,
BUT HOW DO I KNOW
YOU’RE NOT PULLING MY LEG
LIKE YOU ALWAYS DO?
Rohan: EH?
Koichi: HIT THE NAIL
ON THE HEAD, DIDN’T I?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRohan: NO!
I’M BEING COMPLETELY SERIOUS!
THERE’S A DEAD BODY UPSTAIRS!
Koichi: WHAT?!
A REAL DEAD BODY?!
SO, UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
ROHAN-SENSEI?
Rohan: DON’T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
JUST GO ON PAST ME.
PLEASE, KOICHI, YOU HAVE
TO SEE THE BODY. GET GOING.
Koichi: CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT
ALL THIS IS ABOUT? ( gasps )
Rohan: TOLD YOU.
I’M TELLING THE TRUTH.
( gasps ) IT’S GONE!
HOW DID IT JUST DISAPPEAR?!
LOOK, KOICHI. HE’S THERE.
( gasps )
YOU SEE?! IT’S THE MAN!
THIS IS MASAZO KINOTO!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hAFTER HE DIED,
HE TURNED INTO A LIFELESS HUSK!
Koichi: WOW, THAT’S SOME
REALLY IMPRESSIVE WORK.
- NICE JOB.
- ( Rohan gasps )
Koichi: BUT THIS ISN’T THE TIME
TO BE MESSING AROUND.
I KNOW YOU KNOW THAT.
WHILE I’M WITH YOU,
THOSE STAND USERS
THE OLD MAN IN THE PHOTO MADE
ARE TRYING TO HUNT US DOWN.
THE ONLY REASON I RUSHED
ALL THE WAY OVER HERE
WAS BECAUSE I WAS WORRIED
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO YOU!
Rohan: WHY WON’T YOU--
WAIT. THE STAND.
( Cheap Trap chuckles )
Koichi: ANYWAY, JUST BE CAREFUL.
- ( Rohan gasps )
- Koichi: BYE.
Rohan: HOLD ON, KOICHI!
\h\h\h\hDON’T LEAVE!
I ASKED YOU TO COME HERE,
\h\h\h\hBECAUSE I KNEW
THOSE PIECES OF SHIT,
JOSUKE AND OKUYASU,
WOULD JUST LAUGH
AT MY PREDICAMENT!
YOU HAVE TO TRUST ME!
I THOUGHT WE WERE FRIENDS!
KOICHI!
\h\h\h\hCheap Trap:
CHEER UP, BUCKO, YES?
\h\h\h\hDISAPPOINTMENT’S
JUST ANOTHER PART OF LIFE.
Rohan: THIS IS INFURIATING.
\h\h\h\hI’VE NEVER BEEN
SO THOROUGHLY HUMILIATED!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hBASTARD,
YOU’RE GOING TO PAY DEARLY.
♪
♪ SHINING JUSTICE
( singing in Japanese )
♪ BRAND-NEW BED TOWN
♪ LET THE VOICE OF LOVE
TAKE YOU HIGHER ♪
- ♪ HIGHER, HIGHER
- ( singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, BIZARRE SUMMER
( singing in Japanese )
♪ GREAT DAYS
♪
Kira: MY NAILS ARE GOING THROUGH
THEIR SIGNATURE
GROWTH SPURT AGAIN,
AND IT’S NO WONDER WHY.
THE WAY YOUR HANDS RUN THROUGH
THAT PERFECTLY COIFFED HAIR
IS JUST...
CONSIDER YOURSELF LUCKY.
YOU’VE NARROWLY ESCAPED DEATH,
\h\h\h\hAT LEAST UNTIL I FULLY
TRANSITION TO KOSAKU KAWAJIRI.
Minako: MY OLD MAN’S
\h\h\h\hSUCH A PEST.
I CAN’T LEAVE THE HOUSE WITHOUT
THE CRUSTY CODGER FOLLOWING ME.
I EVEN CAUGHT HIM
SPYING ON ME ONCE!
Satoru: MAYBE HE THINKS
YOU’RE OUT PARTYING TOO MUCH.
Minako: AND WHOSE FAULT
WOULD IT BE IF I WAS?
I WAS SO PISSED AT HIM,
I DECIDED TO FREAK HIM OUT
BY SHOPLIFTING RIGHT IN FRONT
OF HIS SAGGY FACE.
THEN I MADE A BEELINE
TO YOUR PLACE,
WHICH I’M SURE SET HIM OFF.
( Satoru laughs )
YOU’RE INSANE, GIRL.
THE COPS ARE PROBABLY
AFTER YOU RIGHT NOW.
( Minako groans ) HEY, YOU,
WHAT’S THE BIG IDEA
TOUCHING PEOPLE’S BAGS?
Satoru: WHAT’S WRONG?
Minako: FORGET IT, BABY.
IT’S NOT WORTH OUR TIME.
Satoru: THE HELL? YOU A PERVERT
OR JUST A DAMN PICKPOCKET?
( fingernails rustle )
Announcer: MORIOH. MORIOH.
Satoru: OH, SHIT, BABE.
LOOK. WE’RE ALREADY IN MORIOH.
COME ON. LET’S GO.
( thump )
OW, THAT FRICKIN’ HURT.
WHAT THE HELL IS YOUR DEAL?
WATCH WHERE YOU’RE WALKIN’,
JERK-OFF!
Minako: YOU SEE
WHAT HE WAS CARRYING?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hIT WAS
A BOWLING-PIN NAIL-CLIPPER.
WHAT KIND OF FREAK CARRIES
AROUND SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
CAN YOU SAY LAME?
( fingernails rustle )
♪
Cheap Trap: YOU’VE GOT
THE PICTURES, YES?
WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU’RE GOING WITH THEM?
Rohan: TO THE MORIOH
\h\h\h\hGRAND HOTEL.
I HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE.
\h\h\h\hCheap Trap:
YOU’RE GOING TO JOTARO?
HE WON’T BE ABLE TO HELP YOU.
YOUR BEST BET IS TO CALL IT
QUITS AND BURN THE PICTURES.
( running footsteps )
- ( Rohan gasping )
- Cheap Trap: IMPRESSIVE,
AND ALL WHILE SOMEONE COULD HAVE
BEEN WATCHING FROM A WINDOW.
THAT WAS VERY RISKY.
♪
THERE. YOU SEE? AT SOME POINT,
ALMOST EVERY STREET
COMES TO AN INTERSECTION.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSEE? SOMEONE
WILL TAKE A PEEK AT YOUR BACK,
SO CROSSING’S IMPOSSIBLE.
AND SINCE THE ROAD
IS ABOUT TO GET WIDER,
THAT MEANS MORE PEOPLE.
LET’S STOP ALL THIS
AND GO BACK, YES?
\h\h\h\hYOU’RE NEVER GOING
TO MAKE IT ACROSS THE ROAD.
Rohan: YOU REALLY THINK SO?
MASAZO KINOTO MADE IT
TO MY HOUSE, DIDN’T HE?
HE’D HAVE HAD TO CROSS
AN INTERSECTION TO DO SO.
I’M SURE I CAN PULL IT OFF, TOO.
I JUST NEED TO KNOW
HOW HE DID IT.
AHA.
LIKE THIS!
THIS CERTAINLY ISN’T
MY MOST SHINING MOMENT,
- BUT IT’LL GET ME ACROSS.
- ( man grunts )
\h\h\h\hCheap Trap:
NOT BAD, ROHAN KISHIBE,
BUT THERE’S SOMETHING
YOU HAVEN’T THOUGHT ABOUT.
WHEN MASAZO KINOTO
WAS CROSSING THE STREET,
I STAYED AS QUIET
AS A CHURCH MOUSE!
HEY, DUMB SHIT,
WHY ARE YOU FARTING ALONG
\h\h\h\hLIKE SOME SLUG?
Man: WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?!
Cheap Trap: SEE? YO!
WHY DON’T YOU TURN AROUND
\h\h\h\hAND FIND OUT?!
Man: YOU’RE PUSHING IT!
\h\h\h\hRohan: THE ONLY ONE
WHO’S MISSING SOMETHING HERE,
CHEAP TRAP, IS YOU.
I HAVE SOMETHING MASAZO DIDN’T,
MY STAND, HEAVEN’S DOOR!
Cheap Trap: WHAT THE...
\h\h\h\hRohan: PERFECT.
NOW THAT THAT’S SETTLED,
I CAN GET TO THE OTHER SIDE.
( Cheap Trap groans )
Rohan: I SUGGEST
YOU PREPARE YOURSELF.
Man: SAY WHAT?
WHAT’S GOIN’ ON HERE?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hCheap Trap:
TRUST ME. YOU’LL NEVER MAKE IT!
WHEN THIS IS OVER,
YOU’LL BE A SHRIVELED-UP
LIMP DICK OF A CORPSE!
Rohan: YOU SURE TALK
\h\h\h\hA GOOD GAME,
BUT THAT’S ALL YOU’RE GOOD AT,
ISN’T IT?
\h\h\h\hYOU WON’T BE
SAYING ANYTHING SOON.
Man: WH-WHO--WHO THE HELL
\h\h\h\hDO YOU THINK
YOU’RE TALKING TO, BITCH?!
WHAT? HUH? UH...
♪
Rohan: SEEMS THERE WON’T BE ANY
MAJOR INTERSECTIONS FOR A WHILE.
( gasps )
Cheap Trap: HEY, DO YOU KNOW
IF YOUR HEAVEN’S DOOR
WORKS ON ANIMALS?
HUH, HUH, DO YOU?
Rohan: YES, IT WORKS
ON ANY INTELLIGENT ANIMAL.
Cheap Trap: WELL, IN THAT CASE,
IF AN ANIMAL SEES YOUR BACK,
IT STANDS TO REASON I’LL
BE ABLE TO TRANSFER TO THEM!
MUCH EASIER THAN PEOPLE, YES?
( Rohan gasps )
( sighs ) THAT’S RIGHT.
\h\h\h\hI’LL HAVE TO BE
JUST AS CAREFUL AROUND THEM.
GOD, I HATE THESE CREATURES.
THEIR GLARE IS INFURIATING.
ALL RIGHT, CAT, BEAT IT!
HOW IN THE--THEY’RE SWARMING!
Cheap Trap: ALL IT TAKES
IS A QUICK GLANCE
\h\h\h\hFROM ANY ONE
OF THESE LITTLE GUYS, YES?
YOU WERE RIGHT WHEN YOU SAID
THE ONLY THING I’M GOOD AT
IS TALKING, YES,
BUT HUMANS AREN’T THE ONLY
LIVING THINGS I CAN TALK TO.
- ( Rohan gasps )
- Cheap Trap: BINGO!
I SUMMONED THOSE ANIMALS HERE!
AND THEY ARE NOT HAPPY CAMPERS.
I JUST FINISHED TELLING THEM
\h\h\h\hTHAT YOU LOVE
KILLING CATS AND DOGS,
SO IMAGINE WHAT THEY THINK!
SIC ’EM, BUDS!
( Rohan yells )
HEAVEN’S DOOR!
\h\h\h\hIT’S NO USE!
THERE ARE TOO MANY OF THEM!
\h\h\h\h- ( dog growls )
- Cheap Trap: YES, I WIN!
Reverb: THREE FREEZE!
( Rohan gasps )
Reverb: THESE ANIMALS
DIDN’T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
TIME TO GET LOST, ALL OF YOU.
SHOO.
Rohan: THAT STAND BELONGS TO...
KOICHI!
Cheap Trap: WHAT?!
Koichi: I THOUGHT YOU WERE
FOOLING ME LIKE ALWAYS,
BUT I HAD THIS NAGGING FEELING,
SO I WENT BACK TO YOUR HOUSE
\h\h\h\hAND FOUND YOU
ACTING JUST AS WEIRD.
EVEN WHEN YOU GOT OUTSIDE,
YOU WERE STILL SKULKING AROUND
THE SIDEWALK
WITH YOUR BACK
AGAINST THE WALL.
\h\h\h\hTHEN THERE’S
HOW YOU CROSSED THE ROAD.
YOU WERE TELLING THE TRUTH ABOUT
THE STAND STUCK TO YOUR BACK.
Rohan: THIS IS WHY I ADMIRE YOU.
YOU’RE THE REAL DEAL, KOICHI,
A TRUE, BLUE FRIEND
TO THE VERY END.
Koichi: IT’S ON YOUR BACK,
SO ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS REMOVE THAT PARASITE
AND WE’RE GOOD TO GO, RIGHT?
REVERB, SPECIAL ABILITY
\h\h\h\hTHREE FREEZE!
( Cheap Trap gasps )
THIS FORCE...
( gags )
( Rohan gasps )
YOU DID IT!
( gasps )
( wails )
Cheap Trap: IT’S NOT THAT EASY.
I’M CLINGING TO YOU
WITH MY SPECIAL ABILITY
AND NOT BRUTE STRENGTH.
IF YOU TRY TO RIP ME OFF,
YOU’LL JUST END UP DESTROYING
YOUR BACK IN THE PROCESS!
NOW TELL KOICHI, YES?
COME ON. YOU BETTER HURRY
\h\h\h\hAND SPIT IT OUT!
Koichi: WHAT, ROHAN-SENSEI?
Rohan: I’M GRATEFUL
TO YOU, KOICHI.
THE FACT THAT YOU WOULD HELP ME
HAS TRULY TOUCHED MY HEART.
BUT I’D APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU’D WITHDRAW ACT THREE.
Koichi: HUH?
Rohan: YOU CAN’T
SEE IT FROM THERE,
BUT IT WOULD SEEM MY BACK
IS STARTING TO RIP ITSELF OPEN.
\h\h\h\h- ( gags )
- ( Koichi gasps )
ACT THREE, WITHDRAW THREE FREEZE
ON THE DOUBLE!
Reverb: S-H-I-T.
WITHDRAW COMPLETED.
\h\h\h\hKoichi: HEY!
YOU OKAY, ROHAN-SENSEI?
HOW BAD IS IT?
\h\h\h\hCheap Trap: HOW BAD
DOES IT LOOK, KOICHI HIROSE?!
YOU’RE THE REASON
HE’S IN THIS MESS!
UNDERSTAND NOW, ROHAN?
YOU CAN’T REMOVE ME.
YOU CAN TRY TO TEAR ME OFF
BY FORCE IF YOU WANT,
BUT YOU’LL END UP TEARING OFF
YOUR OWN BACK ALONG THE WAY!
( Koichi gasps )
( blood squelching )
Cheap Trap: HEY,
\h\h\h\hYOU’RE JUST
GOING TO EXHAUST YOURSELF.
I WONDER, WILL YOU COLLAPSE
FROM THE TRAUMA AND FATIGUE,
OR WILL YOU GO INSANE
AND KILL YOURSELF?
EVEN THE MOST POWERFUL STAND
IN THE WORLD COULDN’T BEAT
THIS WEAKLING’S GIFT FOR GAB
AND UTTER DOMINATION!
( laughs )
YES?
Koichi: A STAND
THAT CLINGS TO BACKS.
THIS IS TOO BIZARRE!
( Rohan chuckles ) BIZARRE.
SO TRUE. HAVE A LOOK.
YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO.
DO IT. ( chuckles )
I’M HAPPY TO GIVE YOU A PEEK.
( both yelp )
( Rohan chuckling )
( crazed laughter )
( Koichi gasps ) ROHAN-SENSEI!
\h\h\h\h- ( gasps )
- ( Rohan laughing )
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hCheap Trap:
HE’S FINALLY LOST HIS MIND!
NOW YOU REALIZE A VISIT
TO JOTARO WOULD BE FUTILE!
Rohan: JOTARO? ( chuckles )
I NEVER HAD ANY INTENTION
OF EVER PAYING HIM A VISIT.
THIS WAS MY DESTINATION.
I WAS BESIDE MYSELF
THAT I FINALLY MADE IT.
I CAN’T HELP BUT LAUGH.
\h\h\h\h( chuckling )
WHAT’S WITH ALL THE RAMBLING?
YOU FINALLY EXPOSED YOUR BACK
TO ANOTHER SOUL!
\h\h\h\hNOW I GET TO FASTEN
TO KOICHI HIROSE! ( laughs )
Koichi: WAIT!
I KNOW THIS STREET!
THIS IS WHERE WE MET...
Rohan: CHEAP TRAP,
\h\h\h\hYOU PICKED A HELL
OF A PLACE TO TURN AROUND.
EVEN IF YOU HAD KNOWN
ABOUT THIS PLACE
AND RESISTED TURNING AROUND,
YOU WOULD’VE STILL HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO LOOK KOICHI’S WAY,
THANKS TO YOUR SPECIAL ABILITY.
Cheap Trap: WH-WHAT THE HELL?!
Koichi: WE’RE WALKING DOWN
REIMI’S STREET!
LOOKING BACK’S A DEATH WISH!
Rohan: YOU WERE RIGHT
ABOUT NO STAND
BEING ABLE TO REMOVE YOU
\h\h\h\hFROM MY BACK.
YOU’D JUST END UP
HURTING ME IF YOU TRIED.
HOWEVER, THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT CAN TAKE YOU,
SOMETHING THAT LATCHES ON
TO THOSE WHO DARE TO LOOK BACK,
\h\h\h\hSOMETHING THAT’LL
CARRY AWAY YOUR VERY SOUL.
( Cheap Trap wails )
\h\h\h\hLET ME GO!
PLEASE LET ME GO, YES?
WHERE ARE THESE THINGS
GONNA TAKE ME?! ANSWER!
Rohan: TO THE OTHER SIDE.
I CAN’T SAY FOR SURE
WHETHER THERE’S
A HEAVEN OR A HELL,
BUT A SIMPLE MEMO
SHOULD DO THE TRICK.
( Cheap Trap screaming )
♪
( Rohan sighs )
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hFOR A STAND
THAT DOES NOTHING BUT TALK,
HE WAS QUITE A LITTLE TERROR.
- KOICHI...
- Koichi: EH?
Rohan: IF YOU HADN’T
HAVE SHOWN UP WHEN YOU DID,
I’M SURE I WOULDN’T STILL
BE AROUND TO TELL THE TALE.
Koichi: I HAD NO CLUE
THIS IS WHERE WE ENDED UP.
\h\h\h\hI WAS TOO FOCUSED
ON THAT FREAKY ENEMY STAND.
( dog barks )
( Koichi gasps ) IT’S REIMI!
\h\h\h\hReimi: HEY, ROHAN,
DID YOU TAKE THESE PICTURES?
Rohan: YES. WHY?
- Reimi: CHECK THIS OUT.
\h\h\h\h- Koichi: HUH?
Reimi: HOW STRANGE.
Minako: OH, DID YOU HEAR?
MIKA GOT HER BOYFRIEND
TO BUY HER A BRAND-NEW PAIR
OF DESIGNER EARRINGS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY YOU BUY ME SOME?
Satoru: MAYBE NEXT TIME.
( gasps ) THE HELL YOU THINK
YOU’RE DOIN’, SKEEZE?!
YOU CAN’T COME IN HERE!
GET OUT OF MY APARTME--
\h\h\h\h- ( gags )
- ( trigger clicks )
( Minako screams )
♪
Kira: HMM. A STUDIO APARTMENT.
MY NAME IS YOSHIKAGE KIRA.
WOULD YOU BE SO KIND
AS TO TELL ME YOUR NAME?
( Minako gasping )
Kira: THEY DON’T LOOK NORMAL,
DO THEY?
LOOK HOW LONG THEY’VE GOTTEN.
DO YOU THINK THERE’S
A SINGLE SOUL ON THE PLANET
WHO CAN KEEP THEIR NAILS
\h\h\h\hFROM GROWING?
THERE ISN’T.
\h\h\h\hNO ONE CAN STOP
A NAIL’S DESTINY TO GROW,
JUST AS THERE’S NO ONE
WHO CAN TRULY SUPPRESS
THE INNER PASSIONS
ONE IS BORN WITH.
NOW I BELIEVE I ASKED YOU
TO TELL ME YOUR NAME.
Minako: WHAT DID YOU DO
TO MY BOYFRIEND?
HE WAS RIGHT HERE BEFORE.
Kira: DON’T EVER ANSWER
A QUESTION WITH A QUESTION!
YOU DID LEARN PROPER ETIQUETTE
WHILE YOU WERE IN SCHOOL,
\h\h\h\hNOW, DIDN’T YOU?
I’M ASKING YOU TO TELL ME
WHAT YOUR NAME IS!
Minako: MINAKO!
MY NAME IS MINAKO!
Kira: HMM. MINAKO.
HMM. WHAT A BEAUTIFUL NAME
YOUR PARENTS BESTOWED UPON YOU.
I APPROVE.
( Minako shuddering )
Kira: MINAKO, I HAVE A LITTLE
REQUEST IF YOU DON’T MIND.
I WOULD BE THRILLED IF YOU
COULD HOLD ON TO THESE FOR ME.
( Minako shuddering )
Kira: AND I’D GREATLY
APPRECIATE IT IF YOU
COULD TRIM MY ROBUST NAILS
WITH THESE LAME CLIPPERS.
YOU’VE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE,
HAVE YOU?
IT’S YOUR LUCKY DAY.
NOW, DON’T CUT THEM TOO SHORT.
- Minako: SOMEONE HELP ME.
- ( clipping )
GOD...
I’M SORRY.
- FORGIVE ME!
- Kira: FORGIVE YOU?
NOW WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
I’M NOT THE LEAST BIT ANGRY,
IF THAT’S WHAT’S CONCERNING YOU.
YOU INTRIGUE ME.
\h\h\h\hI CHOSE YOU
BECAUSE OF OUR CONNECTION.
\h\h\h\hI WAS BORN WITH
A CERTAIN SET OF DESIRES,
\h\h\h\hSO I SIMPLY TRY
TO MAKE THE MOST OF IT.
LIFE’S BETTER THAT WAY.
YOU WERE BEGGING YOUR BOYFRIEND
FOR A PAIR OF EARRINGS, YEAH?
HE LEFT THESE FOR YOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
( Minako shuddering )
( screams )
Kira: YOU TRULY ARE
A DEFT NAIL CUTTER.
HOW I ADORE YOU.
( trigger clicks )
I DARE SAY YOU’RE EVEN CUTER
WHEN YOU’RE SILENT.
SO WHAT TO DO NOW, MY DEAR?
I’D LOVE TO TAKE YOU
BACK HOME WITH ME,
\h\h\h\hBUT I DON’T THINK
THE KAWAJIRIS WOULD APPROVE.
OH, HOW I’VE MISSED
THIS SENSATION.
I FEEL SO COMPLETE.
( Hayato gasping )
TH-THE MAN AND WOMAN
HE FOLLOWED HERE
FROM THE STATION,
HE COMPLETELY VAPORIZED THEM!
Kira: HMM?
♪
HMM.
HMM?
- ( Hayato panting )
- Koichi: WHAT?
THAT’S HAYATO.
WHAT COULD HE BE DOING HERE?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTHIS IS
IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION
FROM THE HOUSE AND SCHOOL.
( gasps ) WHAT’S THAT?
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDAMN IT.
I FORGOT TO LOCK THE DOOR.
( trigger clicks )
COULD HAYATO HAVE...
IT COULDN’T BE.
Hayato: THERE’S NO WAY
\h\h\h\hHE’S HUMAN!
\h\h\h\hWHY IS THAT DEMON
PRETENDING TO BE MY DAD?!
Jotaro: HMM?
♪
THIS MIGHT BE EVIDENCE
THAT HE’S RETURNED.
I’M PRETTY SURE THIS IS BLOOD.
\h\h\h\hSO KIRA’S
FINALLY MADE HIS MOVE.
( door creaks )
♪
Kira: I’M ABSOLUTELY POSITIVE.
\h\h\h\hHAYATO WAS HOLDING
A VIDEO CAMERA IN HIS HAND.
IT DOESN’T SEEM TO BE
ANYWHERE IN HIS ROOM.
HMM. I’VE DEFINITELY NOTICED
HAYATO ACTING STRANGE LATELY.
WHAT IS THAT BOY UP TO?
I HAVE TO FIND OUT.
I NEED TO KNOW FOR SURE.
Hayato: I-I HAVE TO CALM DOWN.
BREATHE, HAYATO. JUST CALM DOWN,
AND GATHER YOUR THOUGHTS.
( gasps )
FIRST, I NEED TO DEAL
WITH THIS TAPE.
SHOULD I SHOW IT TO SOMEONE?
IT CAN’T BE MOM.
\h\h\h\hSHE HAS COMPLETE
AND TOTAL FAITH IN THE GUY.
SHOULD I SHOW IT TO THE POLICE?
WOULD THEY BELIEVE
THAT I WITNESSED A MAN
BEING VAPORIZED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME?
WHAT AM I SAYING?
HE’S NOT A NORMAL HUMAN.
\h\h\h\hCOULD THE POLICE
EVEN CATCH SOMEONE LIKE HIM?
IS THERE ANYONE IN THE WORLD
WHO HAS WHAT IT TAKES
TO CATCH A MONSTER LIKE HIM?
WHAT DO I DO? SOONER OR LATER,
HE’S GONNA KILL MOM AND ME.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?!
( door opens )
( gasps )
♪
( shudders )
Kira: EVENING.
IS THERE ANY ROOM
IN THERE LEFT FOR ME?
( Hayato gasps )
Kira: CAN DEAR OLD DAD JOIN YOU?
WHY THE ODD FACE?
WE’VE DONE THIS BEFORE.
( Hayato gasping )
OH, I WAS ACTUALLY
JUST FINISHING UP, AND--
Kira: DON’T BE SILLY.
I AM YOUR FATHER.
WE SHOULD DO SOME BONDING.
Hayato: WHAT’S HE
PLANNING TO DO?
IF HE FINDS THIS TAPE,
\h\h\h\hIT’S ALL OVER.
Kira: SORRY TO BE A BOTHER,
BUT I’LL NEED TO USE THAT BUCKET
FOR THE BATH.
\h\h\h\h- Hayato: HUH?
- Kira: I’D LIKE TO WASH
THE LONG DAY AWAY
WITH SOME WATER.
\h\h\h\hHayato: NO!
SINCE WE’RE BONDING,
I’LL WASH YOUR BACK
FOR YOU, DAD! ( laughs )
Kira: HMM? WHAT A SPLENDID IDEA.
BUT PLEASE ALLOW ME
TO WASH YOUR BACK FIRST.
Hayato: HUH?
Kira: YOU’VE BEEN
IN THE BATH FOR A WHILE,
SO IT’S ONLY FAIR.
WE CAN JUST TAKE TURNS.
HOW DOES THAT SOUND?
HERE. SIT.
( Hayato panting )
Kira: WHAT IS IT?
\h\h\h\hYOU’RE SWEATING
LIKE A GUILTY LITTLE PIG
RIPE FOR SLAUGHTER.
DID THE HEAT GET TO YOU?
Hayato: NO, I’M FINE.
\h\h\h\hKira: JUST LOOK
AT THE WAY YOU’RE SHAKING.
YOU CAN’T BE FINE.
IT’D BE RATHER ODD
FOR A PERSON TO TREMBLE
AFTER BEING IN THE BATH
\h\h\h\hFOR TOO LONG.
Hayato: HEY, CUT IT OUT, DAD,
THAT TICKLES!
YOU CAN’T TOUCH MY BACK THERE,
BECAUSE I FREAK OUT.
I’VE ONLY TOLD YOU
A MILLION TIMES!
Kira: EH?
( growls )
HOW SILLY OF ME. YOU’RE RIGHT.
\h\h\h\hYOU ALWAYS WERE
A TICKLISH ONE, HAYATO.
Hayato: UH, I’LL TAKE CARE
OF THE FRONT MYSELF.
Kira: I’D BE HAPPY
TO LEND YOU A HAND.
BY THE WAY, I WANTED TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTHIS EVENING,
I WAS DOING SOME WORK ERRANDS
IN THE OPPOSITE END
OF TOWN NEAR JOZENJI
- WHEN I HAPPENED TO SEE YOU.
- Hayato: HUH?!
Kira: AND YOU WERE HOLDING
A VIDEO CAMERA.
\h\h\h\hWHAT COULD YOU
HAVE BEEN DOING THERE?
- ( Hayato gasping )
- Kira: I’VE GOT HIM.
I KNEW THIS SLEUTHING SHIT
WAS SPYING ON ME!
I CAN’T BELIEVE IT.
\h\h\h\hSO MUCH FOR CASUALLY
ASSIMILATING INTO THIS FAMILY.
IT HAS BEEN ONE CATASTROPHE
AFTER ANOTHER, A YEAR OF HELL.
KILLING THIS PUNK
WILL CAUSE A COMMOTION
AND A BAD ONE AT THAT,
BUT HE SAW EVERYTHING.
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
A STRAND OF THIS BRAT’S HAIR
NOW FUNCTIONS AS A BOMB.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hALL IT’LL TAKE
IS A SMALL BLAST TO HIS SKULL,
AND IT’LL APPEAR HE SIMPLY
SLIPPED AND BUMPED HIS HEAD.
\h\h\h\hPEOPLE SLIP AND FALL
IN THE BATHROOM ALL THE TIME,
\h\h\h\hSO IT’S TIME
FOR YOU TO DIE, PEST!
Hayato: SO YOU
GONNA KILL ME, TOO?
( Deadly Queen grunts )
Hayato: TAKE A LOOK
AROUND, "POPS."
I’M RECORDING EVERYTHING
THAT’S HAPPENING!
Kira: WHAT? ( grunts )
( Hayato grunts )
I’VE NEVER TRUSTED YOU, FRAUD!
\h\h\h\hI’VE RECORDED
ALL YOUR WEIRD SHOE SIZES
AND SIGNATURE
PRACTICING SESSIONS!
AND THAT’S NOT ALL.
I TAPED THAT CAT PLANT
LIVING IN THE ATTIC, TOO!
\h\h\h\hONLY I KNOW
WHERE ALL THE TAPES ARE,
BUT IF SOMETHING TERRIBLE
WERE TO HAPPEN TO ME,
\h\h\h\hI’M SURE SOMEONE
WOULD FIND THEM EVENTUALLY.
Kira: WHERE DO YOU GET OFF--
Hayato: YOU’RE NOT GONNA
LAY A FINGER ON ME! WE CLEAR?!
Kira: HOW DARE YOU?!
YOU THINK YOU CAN THREATEN
THE LIKES OF ME?
Hayato: AND THAT
GOES DOUBLE FOR MOM!
( Kira growls )
♪