♪
woman: I was
in community college
when I first crossed paths
with that buzz-kill of a man
I call my husband.
It turned out he went
to one of the ritzier colleges
in the area.
My friends at the time
thought he was dreamy
and fawned over the guy.
The fact that I was
the girl on his arm
made me feel a bit superior.
- ( Door opens )
- ( Gasps )
( Door closes )
Then we had a kid.
boy: I get it.
Because it’s three times faster,
the picture quality is...
Woman: Oh, come on, hayato.
At least say, "hi."
Hayato: Hi, mom.
( Door opens, closes )
( Woman sighs )
it’s not that
my husband’s a bad person.
He’s not even a heavy drinker.
And he might not bring home
a big paycheck,
but he’s a damn hard worker.
Even so, I fell into a marriage
without ever knowing love.
- hmm?
- ( Lock clicks )
Huh. So he’s finally home.
All I ever hear is,
"where’s dinner?"
"Make me a bath,"
"i’m going to bed."
Jeez. What a bore.
♪
Man: I’m home.
Where’s dinner?
Shinobu: Oh, hey,
you’re finally home.
I didn’t even hear you
open the door.
Sorry. I was too busy to cook.
That’ll have to do.
But your favorite’s
on the table.
I bet he’s pissed.
Let’s see if he’s man enough
to do something about it.
Who am I kidding?
You’re gonna sit there
stuffing your face in silence
like you always do.
singers:
♪ mori, mori, mori, mori
- ♪ morioh Cho radio
- ( Shinobu chuckles )
Singers: ♪ morioh Cho radio
Kai: Good evening!
This is morioh radio.
Kai harada here,
your neighborhood purveyor
of good vibes.
Shinobu: Hey, what you
doin’ over there?
Kai: How is everyone on this
fine night? Great, I hope.
Allow me to ease you
into a mellow evening.
Koichi: We found his house
about 15 minutes away
from morioh station.
It was in a part of town
known for its views and villas.
Actually, it was
his former house,
where he lived
as yoshikage Kira.
Now he has a new face,
a new job,
a new place to call home,
and probably even a new family.
It’s obvious that he’s
never turning up here again.
Okuyasu: What if
we find a dead body?
Koichi: But just the same,
we still have
to search the place.
If we’re going to find any clues
as to where
this "new man" ran off to,
we’re going to find them
right here in this house.
Josuke: Huh? Eh?
given how much
that kid looks like our guy,
this must be his album.
Jotaro: Yoshikage Kira.
He was born in morioh
on January 30, 1966.
He’s nearly two meters tall,
he weighs 65 kilograms,
and his blood type is a.
He was born to older parents.
When he was 21, his father,
yoshihiro, fell ill and died.
Seems his mother
died soon after.
graduated in 1988
with a degree in literature.
Same year, he starts
at kameyu in s city
and, in 1993, transfers
to the morioh branch.
He has no previous
criminal record,
has never married,
has no close friends or lover.
He’s never even had a surgery.
And we can’t find him
with fingerprints,
dental records,
or surgical scars.
Josuke: So what
you’re trying to say
is we’ve reached a dead end.
Josuke: Check it out.
The trophies and plaques,
they all say third place,
so he certainly
wasn’t a star athlete.
Nothing speaks to his talents.
Was it sports? Music? Writing?
even here,
he’s trying not to stand out.
he’s never been
the object of ridicule or envy,
and he never reveals
his strengths
or weaknesses to anyone.
Josuke: Which means...
Jotaro: It’s all
been a deception.
he’s been hiding
his talent and intellect.
He knew laying low would be
the best way
to stay out of trouble.
My hope in coming here
was to find
hobbies or interests,
any clue in the slightest.
Jotaro: Hobbies?
I may have found one.
For some weird reason, he keeps
a bunch of jars in this drawer.
You see?
If you ask me, this looks like
a collection of bonito flakes.
But what is with the numbers?
"1983." hmm, must be the year.
( Lid pops )
( Sniffs )
P.u. They smell rancid.
What are they?
Jotaro: Seems they’re
fingernail clippings.
Josuke: Huh?
( Screams )
whose nails
do you think they are?!
( Gasps ) Hold on.
jotaro: Calm down.
They’re not from his victims.
Those clippings are his own.
He kept meticulous notes
on the subject.
Jotaro: Notes? You mean
those numbers on the jars?
You mean he’s been collecting
these things since 1983?
That’s 15 years of yuck!
( Gasps ) There are
details about every finger!
According to this, in 1983,
his right thumb grew a nail
that was
31 1/2 centimeters long!
Wait a sec! I’m pretty sure 1983
was the year
reimi sugimoto was murdered!
Jotaro: Yeah, and the records
begin in that year.
He probably reached a point
where he couldn’t repress his
murderous impulses any longer.
Josuke: Whoa!
this is all the info
he collected about his toenails!
Jotaro: Our boring office worker
seems to have
a very interesting hobby.
Look.
This is a form of divination.
it’s similar
to ancient Jewish merchants,
who once observed sunspots
to predict economic prospects.
It appears yoshikage Kira
is tying his nail growth
to his physical and
mental preparedness.
His preparedness to kill,
that is.
( Josuke gasps ) Check out 1999!
By June of this year,
they’d already grown
over 20 centimeters!
I knew he was crazy,
but this is sick!
Jotaro: I agree with you,
but this won’t help us
track him down.
there might be
something else we can use.
- ( Camera whirs )
- ( Both gasp )
Josuke: What the hell, jotaro?
You think someone’s
skulking around the house
under our noses?
Jotaro: Seems that way.
Josuke, stay on guard.
Josuke: Could he have been
maybe working with a partner?
jotaro: No way.
He’s too cautious for that.
more people
means more risk for capture.
A partner could
just rat him out.
He wouldn’t even consider it.
Josuke: Is that...
Jotaro...
Quickly, look at the camera.
( Jotaro grunts )
( Gasps ) No doubt about it.
That’s kira’s father!
Josuke: He’s behind us,
just sitting in the corner!
Where’d he go?!
That’s really freaky!
We’re in a shitload of trouble!
Are we actually
dealing with a ghost?
jotaro: Yeah.
Considering reimi’s situation,
it’s entirely possible
that his father
is stuck in some kind
of spiritual limbo
between the land of the living
and the dead.
Look at his expression.
It seems like he wants us
to make a quick exit.
- ( Telephone rings )
- ( Josuke gasps )
( Ring )
Hey, are you trying
to give us the willies
with your spooky ghost energy?
This sucks,
but we can’t leave with all
this paranormal shit goin’ on.
yoshihiro:
Answer the damn phone, slacker!
Can’t you hear me callin’?!
( Both gasp )
( Josuke grunting )
Yoshihiro: You think my face
is saying, "take a hike"?
Well, you couldn’t be
more wrong!
You were looking
at the face of a man
who will never allow you
to leave this house alive!
i’ll kill you
for going after my son.
Josuke: Old fart! Do you know
about all the crimes
your son has committed?
okuyasu:
Hey, you guys, what’s with
all the racket in here?
Is something wrong?
Josuke: Where the hell
are you hiding?!
Show yourself,
you geriatric ghost!
- ( Okuyasu gasps )
- Koichi: There’s a ghost?!
( Gasps )
Jotaro: Josuke, I don’t
think he’s hiding at all.
Kira’s father has been
in the room the entire time,
watching us.
You see?
josuke:
Wh-when the hell did he...
jotaro: He’s able
to move around in the picture,
so it stands to reason
he made the call from in there,
and he threw the phone at you
from inside the picture as well.
Yoshihiro: I’ll kill you.
if you dare
go after my dearest son,
i’ll murder you!
( Both gasp )
- Koichi: Hey, josuke!
- ( Josuke gasps )
Koichi: Even if we can’t
physically fight a ghost,
our stands can!
On the day we met reimi,
Rohan-sensei used heaven’s door
to read her memories!
Josuke: Good to know!
How do you like this?
♪
What?!
- ( Both gasp )
- ( Josuke screaming )
Jotaro: Damn it! Damage
inflicted on the photograph
backfires to us!
Fix it now, josuke,
- or we’ll be ripped to shreds!
- ( Shining diamond yells )
( Yoshihiro yelps )
Koichi: Thank goodness
you guys are back to normal!
Yoshihiro: Those powers.
Yes, it’s all making sense.
you whelps have
special abilities like my son!
Josuke: Okuyasu, it’s time
for you to do your thing!
- okuyasu: Huh?
- Josuke: You have to hurry up
and use the hand
to cut this crusty old man
out of the picture!
( Okuyasu gasps ) Got you!
You just leave everything
to me, josuke!
- ( Groans )
- Josuke: Huh?
( Koichi yells )
( Okuyasu groans )
( Josuke gasps ) Okuyasu?!
What the hell happened?
How’d I run straight into
the window? That’s so weird!
( Jotaro gasps )
( Koichi gasping )
what the heck?!
Do you guys see my hands?!
They’re over there!
There’s something stopping me
from coming
into the room with you!
( Josuke growls )
( Gasps ) What in the hell?
Shining diamond: Dora!
Josuke: I don’t know how,
but there’s an invisible wall
blocking anyone from entering!
And I don’t think
I can break it! Shit!
Yoshihiro: I see you’ve
finally figured it out.
( Laughs )
This photo is special.
the invisible wall
that you’re so worked up about
is actually
the edge of this picture.
( Both gasp )
Yoshihiro: I’m a ghost
who lives out his days
in a photograph.
I can control the space of
any picture in which I appear.
By using that camera,
I trap a person’s spiritual
energy within a photograph.
That’s my power!
The room you’re in
is inside the picture!
Damaging the photo
means damaging
the spiritual energy, too,
which won’t end well for you!
Okuyasu: But that doesn’t
make a lick of sense.
How are we in the picture
if i’m looking right at it?
Yoshihiro: You’re clearly
not the brightest,
so i’ll spell it out for you.
After I kill these two fools,
i’ll ensnare you and the brat
and shred you to pieces!
Koichi: J-josuke! Mr. Jotaro!
( Gasps )
( Yoshihiro laughs )
Time to die.
Josuke: Bastard!
Get us out of here right now!
Jotaro, why are you
just standing around?!
Your star platinum
is super powerful,
so hurry up, and do something!
Jotaro: Sorry, josuke,
but i’m gonna
- have to throw in the towel.
- Josuke: Huh?!
jotaro: Stopping
that old-timer’s attacks
is downright impossible.
Every bit of damage
we throw at him
will only come right back to us.
Star platinum could stop time,
but there’s really no point.
It’d be a waste of energy.
Josuke: I can’t believe it.
What are you saying?
Have you completely
lost your mind?!
Yoshihiro: Die! Die! Die!
( Josuke gasps )
♪
Yoshihiro: Your heads have
got some good spin to ’em!
Josuke: Great. He’s got a knife.
( Shining diamond yells )
( Grunts ) Dora! Dora!
Josuke: It’s not working!
I can’t touch it, jotaro!
Jotaro: I’ve given up on
stopping the geezer. However...
Yoshihiro: Wha?
♪
Jotaro: If he’s being honest
and can really control
any photograph he’s in...
Then maybe the best way to win
is to take a shot of him so he’s
in the picture by himself.
Yoshihiro: What the?!
( Josuke gasping )
( Sighs )
Yoshihiro: You found a way
to sidestep my attack entirely.
- damn it!
- Jotaro: Why don’t you
give our friend here
a nice send-off?
And make sure you add
a little bit of style to it.
Jotaro: Huh?
Uh, it looks like
you weren’t so big and bad
after all, fool!
Yoshihiro: I underestimated you,
but I see
you’re seasoned fighters.
You’ve got lots of experience
battling opponents
with special abilities,
like my son, don’t you?!
Josuke: Remember,
the old fart’s a ghost!
He can get out of the picture!
( Yoshihiro yells )
Star platinum: Ora!
Yoshihiro: Eep!
♪
( Yoshihiro grunting )
Jotaro: We need to make sure
you behave yourself
and stay put.
There’s something in this house
you really
don’t want us to find.
That’s why you’re attacking us
with so much fervor, isn’t it?
( Yoshihiro gags )
( Shrieks )
Okuyasu: Oh, I get it.
if you fold
that crusty old prune in half,
there’s no way he can get out.
Looks like we win this one.
Jotaro: Okuyasu and koichi,
search this room.
Josuke and I have got this one.
( Yoshihiro gasping )
I can’t protect my son
if i’m trapped in here!
What am I gonna do?
If it falls into their hands,
it’s all over!
♪
Josuke: Huh?
Koichi: What could he be hiding
that’s so important,
he’d do all this
to keep us from finding it?
Okuyasu: I don’t have
the foggiest clue,
but i’m not gonna sweat it.
If the old man turns white
as a sheet, we should be good.
Yoshihiro: Help me!
I can’t breathe!
It’s torture in here!
Can’t I have a bit of air?!
Just poke a couple
of holes in the tape,
and let me catch my breath.
What? You seriously
can’t breathe in there?
Okuyasu: He’s pulling
your leg, koichi.
Don’t fall for it.
he wants you to make
an opening so he can get away.
Yoshihiro: I know
you don’t trust me,
but I really
am dying in here, I swear!
Koichi: I don’t know
about this, okuyasu.
I’m claustrophobic,
so I sorta get what
the poor guy’s going through.
okuyasu: Oh,
quit your bitchin’, geezer.
if you really need
a breathing hole that bad...
I’m more than happy to help.
Here. How’s that
working out for you?
I know it’s a little tacky.
( Chuckles )
Yoshihiro: What do you
think you’re doing?!
- ( Okuyasu laughs )
- Yoshihiro: Damn it!
Get me out of here,
you wretched little punk!
Okuyasu: Sounds like you
caught your breath. ( Laughs )
those tacks
ain’t goin’ nowhere, gramps.
Yoshihiro: Tacks, you say?
that must mean
you stuck me to the post.
- ( Both gasp )
- ( Yoshihiro laughs )
What a red-letter day.
You idiots don’t realize it,
but those tacks
are my ticket out of here!
( Okuyasu gasps )
Yoshihiro: I couldn’t have
planned it better myself.
Much obliged, suckers. So long!
( Pounding )
okuyasu: Hey,
you pruny old bastard!
what the hell
was that sound just now?!
What did you do?!
Open your mouth, damn it!
I’m talking to you!
koichi: I think
we might have messed up!
What if he really used
the tacks to escape?
( Okuyasu gasps )
Koichi: Mr. Jotaro!
- Kira’s father got away!
- ( Jotaro gasps )
Okuyasu: This mess is
only happening cause of me!
I stuck some tacks in it,
and he did something weird!
Eh? Wha?
Yoshihiro: Heh! You’ve been
duped, my blockhead friend!
That was a battle of wits,
and you lost!
( Okuyasu gasps )
You mean he was faking?!
( Koichi gasps )
( Josuke gasps )
There’s no way.
i mean,
this is the bow and arrow,
but why is it here?
I just don’t understand.
We already retrieved them
from otoishi!
I thought the speedwagon
foundation was guarding them.
What’s going on?
Is this another set?
Jotaro: Hey, watch out!
Kira’s father has escaped!
( Josuke gasps )
- ( Yoshihiro grunts )
- Josuke: Damn it!
Yoshihiro: This is
the very arrow
that brought forth deadly queen.
Whoever wields it
holds all the power!
I’ll never let you
take it from me!
( All gasping )
( Bird squawking )
( Yoshihiro laughs )
( Koichi gasps )
Josuke: Use reverb, koichi!
Sic act one on him!
koichi: I can’t!
He’s already too far away!
Josuke: Frickin’ great!
At least now we know
what kira’s father was
trying to stop us from finding!
he was hiding
another bow and arrow!
( Okuyasu panting )
Damn it! It’s all my fault!
Jotaro: No, okuyasu.
He simply outsmarted us.
that geezer’s
definitely kira’s father.
There’s no mistaking it.
They’re gonna fight
to survive at all costs.
Their unrelenting resolve is
what’s getting the best of us.
( Yoshihiro laughs )
As long as those chumps don’t
get this arrow, we’ll be fine.
And in the meantime, i’ll use it
to make even more enemies
for them to face!
Jotaro: The bow and arrow.
So it’s true.
I had a feeling there
might be more than one set.
That would explain
how dio and his henchmen
were able to pull together
such a large group
of stand users so quickly.
They built an army of minions
across the globe
using multiple sets
of bows and arrows.
- ( Okuyasu gasps )
- ( Josuke swallows )
Jotaro: Kira’s father
probably obtained this set
from enyaba the witch,
and we already know
okuyasu’s brother keicho
came into possession of one
at some point
before they arrived in morioh.
Stand users really do seem
to be drawn to each other.
Yoshihiro: Oh, yoshikage,
where are you?
Even as a little boy,
you couldn’t repress
your urges to kill women.
but if that’s
what makes you happy,
i’ll support and protect you.
That’s my duty
as a parent, so...
( Bird squawking )
As you’re my one and only son,
i’ll do all I can for you.
Shinobu: I can’t say i’ve ever
seen this side of you before.
I mean, since when do you know
your way around a kitchen?
it’s not
some kind of prank, is it?
There’s two plates here,
so I assume one’s mine.
You can’t possibly think i’d eat
something you slopped together.
That’s insane.
( Clippers snipping )
Seriously?
Do you really think now is
the best time to cut your nails?
Besides, you cut them
last night, didn’t you?
They sure grow fast.
holy shit!
This is actually delicious.
♪
( Cat meowing )
( Window rattling )
( Shinobu gasps ) Kitty!
How’d you get out there?
Were you out here in this tree
crying all night
because you couldn’t
get back into the house?
- ( Shower running )
- We need to talk!
You closed that stupid window
near the tree, didn’t you?
Kira: Hmm.
Shinobu: How many times
am I gonna have to tell you
to leave it open?!
( Kitty meows, hisses )
Shinobu: Oh, my goodness.
What’s the matter, sweetie?
Why are you getting
so worked up?!
( Kitty screeching )
( Handle squeaks )
Kira: I guess cats aren’t
the biggest fans of water.
My apologies. I wasn’t thinking
and acted carelessly.
Sorry. It won’t happen again.
( Shinobu gasps )
There’s definitely something
strange going on with him.
First he starts cooking for me
out of the blue,
and now he’s
using an actual blade
instead of his electric razor.
Blades always
give him razor burn.
- ( Doorbell rings )
- ( Gasps )
Man: Listen, pal!
You still haven’t paid
last month’s rent,
you cheapskate!
Now you owe for this month,
so fork over the yen!
Not leaving ’til i’m paid!
( Shinobu gasps )
Kira: Rent?
Shinobu: You heard the man.
Go and get the money
from the safe
before he kicks us out.
Kira: Right. The safe.
Shinobu: Get a move on!
What are you waiting for?
You have the combination!
( Kira gasping )
( Shinobu gasps )
What are you doing?!
Get back up here!
Kira: Thank you
for taking the time
to drop by this morning,
but I appear
to be running a bit short
on cash at the moment.
I’m sure you understand.
Landlord: Huh?
All that hair gel must be
seeping into your noggin!
I should have known
you young deadbeats
wouldn’t be able to afford
my gorgeous home!
that’s what I get for
doing business with schmucks!
Learn to live
within your means!
Shinobu: You’ll get your money--
kira: No, I think
you misunderstood me earlier.
I said I was short on cash,
but I meant that I only had
a little over 500,000.
- Landlord: Ah!
- ( Shinobu gasps )
Kira: I’ll only be able
to pay for this month,
last month, and for the next
couple of months in advance.
Will that suffice for now?
Landlord: Yes,
that’ll do nicely.
thanks so much.
Have a good one. ( Chuckles )
Until next time.
( Door closes )
Shinobu: Wh-what was that?
I don’t know how,
but you must
have stolen that money.
there’s no point
trying to say that you didn’t.
you stole it from
the landlord’s bag, didn’t you?
if anyone else
was in this situation,
they’d be horrified that their
partner could do such a thing,
but his gusto,
the way he stole the money
and lied about it so easily...
I’ve been with him
for so many years,
but he’s never made me
feel like this before.
It’s exhilarating.
It’s like i’m falling in love
with him for the first time.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪