( Josuke gasps )
( Rohan slams table )
Don’t lay a finger
on those dice,
josuke higashikata!
( Josuke gasps )
Rohan: I would stay put
if I were you.
Josuke: I wonder
what he’s gonna do?
If he finds out i’ve been
cheating this whole time,
well, let’s just say
a simple apology
won’t be enough
to smooth things over.
Rohan: Hmm.
Josuke: What exactly
is the problem?
Rohan: It might be
my mind playing tricks,
but I could swear
the dice are staring at me.
( Mikitaka gulps )
Ba-dum, ba-dum.
( Rohan scoffs )
Well, at any rate,
let’s get back to the game.
josuke: Wow,
you’re way braver than I am.
It’ll just be two for me.
Catch my drift now, Mr. Alien?
I know the point is
to come out on top,
but I only have to do that
by a little bit.
All right, go!
It’s like what i’m saying
is going in one ear
and out the other!
- ( Gasps )
- ( Rohan chuckles )
Guess that’s what you call
a streak of luck, eh?
( Laughs )
Rolling that score again
isn’t impossible.
( Josuke gasps )
rohan: An omen is worth
five times the initial bet, yes?
Here you go.
The dice will roll as they may.
( Chuckles )
( Josuke chuckles ) Guess so.
You can never predict these
kinds of things. Am I right?
( Rohan laughing )
( Josuke laughing )
( Gasps )
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
( josuke gasping )
Wh-wha--
what the hell
do you think you’re doing?!
Rohan: I don’t quite
know how, but it’s clear
that you’ve been cheating me
from the start.
Damn it. Not being able to
figure it out is unacceptable.
Josuke: Hold on! That’s why
you stabbed yourself?!
Rohan: You’re insufferable.
However, for Mr. Joestar
and koichi’s sakes,
i’ve been keeping my cool
where you’re concerned,
but that ends now.
Cheating me crosses
every line ever drawn.
I’m sure you’ve been gloating
this entire time,
and the thought of it
makes me sick.
Josuke: Just give me your hand.
I’ll have shining diamond
fix it for you.
- then we can--
- Rohan: Shut your mouth!
Do you have any idea why
I did that to my little finger?
So you can’t back out
of the game like a coward,
josuke higashikata!
you’re just
a pea-brained dullard!
i refuse to let you
disrespect the great Rohan!
Each of us is going
to have one more turn.
And as we play, i’ll find a way
to see through
your immoral deceptions,
but if I fail
to uncover the truth
behind your
clandestine tactics,
here’s two million yen.
Consider it monetary incentive
to receive treatment from
shining diamond after the game.
However, if I do unveil
the nature of your deception,
your little finger will belong
to me, josuke higashikata.
( Josuke gasps )
Tamami: Hey! Looks like you two
are having
a ripsnortin’ good time!
♪
Tamami: Yo, josuke, what’s up?
Long time, no see!
I’ve been stuck in that stupid
hospital for a month now.
I’m still kinda fuzzy
on the details,
but i’m told I conked my noggin
on the side of the road.
Josuke: Tamami? What the heck
are you poking your nose
around here for?
rohan: I hired him
to be a repo man of sorts,
just as a precaution.
Josuke: Repo man?
Tamami: Sorry to keep
you boys waiting,
but i’m here
and ready to serve.
And not to worry. I’m prepared.
My trusty soul-affixing lock
will ensure you receive
what we agreed on.
( Josuke gasps )
Tamami: I will fulfill my duty,
regardless of who the Victor is.
You have my word.
my fee’s whichever
is the greatest, 400k or 20%.
You’ll both play one more round,
while Rohan tries to figure out
how you’re cheating him.
- Isn’t that right?
- Rohan: Yes.
Josuke: What?!
Rohan: Although,
there’s a chance
you could be tempted
to withhold your trick,
so I will simply ensure
that you don’t.
should you win
without your usual deceptions,
tamami’s lock will activate
and automatically
attach itself to your body.
Josuke: Now i’m
really up shit creek.
It’s now or never.
I’ve gotta pull off this trick
and get myself out of this mess.
Rohan: If we’re clear,
i’ll roll first.
Get ready.
Here it comes!
Tamami: A four!
Two threes and a four!
( Rohan growls )
Josuke: Thank god.
A normal result for once.
He won’t figure it out now.
( Rohan groans )
Josuke: So it’s
my turn now, right?
( Rohan scoffs )
Seems like a weight’s
been lifted
off your shoulders.
It’s almost as though a task
you requested of someone
was a success.
( Josuke gasps )
Just stay calm.
Rohan still doesn’t have a clue.
I can do this.
Eh?
♪
( Mikitaka gags )
Josuke: What in the--
guh! Is that barf?
Oh, shit. He’s getting dizzy.
I bet it’s ’cause Rohan
was shaking him so much.
Rohan: Not so fast. I insist
you stop covering the dice.
I can’t see them if they’re
in your hand like that.
Shake the dice
with your palm open.
( Josuke gasps )
- ( Siren blaring )
- Tamami: Huh?
Must be a fire somewhere.
( Siren blaring )
( Josuke gasps ) What?
- Sirens?!
- Tamami: Huh?
Josuke: That’s right.
he’s allergic
to the sound of sirens.
at this rate,
he’ll revert back to normal.
What is the holdup?
Quit your stalling!
Show me what you’re holding
in your hand!
( Josuke yells )
You just heard the way
i get myself
hyped up for battle!
Now get ready to lose!
Do it! Go!
- ( Tamami gasps )
- ( Rohan gasps )
Tamami: It’s a 666 omen!
And the lock didn’t activate!
Josuke’s a lowdown,
rotten cheater!
( Sirens blaring )
( Rohan groans )
Tamami: So how about it?
Did you figure it out,
rohan-sensei?
( Rohan groans )
( Sirens blaring )
( Josuke gasps )
Tamami: Well, what’s the word?
Does your silence mean
you’re throwin’ in the towel?
( Rohan groans )
Josuke: Looks like
those weird little dots
aren’t on rohan’s side.
hang in there.
Tamami: Well, don’t leave us
here in suspense!
Did you figure it out or not?
( Mikitaka gags )
Josuke: Shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit, shit.
Tamami: That’s it! Of course!
It all makes sense!
Josuke: Damn. I’m toast.
Tamami: I’ve got it!
The fire’s here!
- Rohan: Huh?
- Tamami: Rohan-sensei,
your house is
burning to the ground!
Josuke: Eh?
Tamami: It was
the magnifying glass.
The sunlight went through it
and started the fire!
We were distracted
and didn’t notice!
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Rohan: Shut up!
I don’t care if the house
ends up in a heap of ash.
All that matters here
is figuring out
how josuke is cheating!
Tamami: Don’t be ridiculous!
Just take your two million,
and get the hell outta here!
josuke: Well,
I think i’ll be going now.
Rohan: Hey! Come back!
Josuke: But before I go,
i’ll fix that finger of yours.
Rohan: Ohh. You can’t just
heal people without permission!
Josuke, wait! You bastard!
Josuke: That was a close one!
I guess i’m the kind of guy
that some people
just love to hate, huh?
Who would have figured?
Mikitaka: What’s wrong?
You seem displeased.
tell me, was I
of adequate assistance to you?
Josuke: Could you,
like, shut up?! Jeez!
Narrator: Rohan kishibe’s house,
half burned, and 7 million yen
in fire damage.
Josuke may have
escaped unscathed,
but he managed to find
himself even further
on rohan’s bad side.
singers:
♪ mori, mori, mori, mori
♪ morioh Cho radio
Kai: Just a friendly reminder
to all you drivers out there
to be extra careful
when you’re on the road.
It seems a motorcycle crashed
at the entrance
of futatsumori tunnel yesterday,
and the young rider
was badly injured.
Police later discovered
that the accident...
Hayato: Mom’s been
acting different lately.
She’s been dressing up,
wearing new lipstick.
She’s happy.
Did something happen?
Interesting.
Mom doesn’t usually
get naked in front of dad,
not in that way.
( Recording whirring )
Sometimes I wonder
if I was born to parents
with no love for each other.
( Gasps )
What’s he doing?
Kira: Josuke higashikata,
jotaro kujo,
they’re the reason
i’m in this predicament.
♪
( Josuke yawns )
mikitaka: Eh?
Oh, josuke, it’s you.
Thank you again.
Josuke: Hey, man, no prob.
So, did you find a place
to sleep and get a bite to eat?
Woman: Mikitaka! Mikitaka!
get your heinie
over here this instant!
We haven’t been
in town that long,
and there are lots errands
to be done, young man.
Mikitaka: Of course.
Sorry, mother. I’m coming.
Josuke: Huh? Mother?
Woman: Oh, for pete’s sake.
Are you telling people
that you’re an alien again?
What have I told you
about playing these pranks?
i do apologize
if my boy has been a bother.
They actually took him seriously
at his school in Tokyo.
You should have seen
the ruckus he caused.
( Laughs )
Now, if you’ll excuse us.
Josuke: Huh? What?
Mikitaka: I brainwashed her.
Isn’t that great?
As far as she knows,
i’m her son.
Mikitaka hazekura is my alias
while i’m here on earth.
So long for now!
mrs. Hazekura:
Mikitaka! It’s time to go!
( Josuke gasping )
Yoshihiro: What the hell
is going on here?
Just who the devil
was that oddball?
Was he serious
about being an alien,
or was he simply
a stand user I created
when I threw the arrow
and cut his neck?
the way that boy
was able to drive a wedge
between josuke and Rohan was
certainly a sight to behold,
but he’s out.
Next they’ll face the stand,
highway go go!
it’ll crush
whoever hunts my son.
Josuke: Eh?
Rohan: Hmm?
( Josuke gasps )
rohan: Are you
just going to ignore me?
The least you could do is
say hello. It’s common courtesy
to address those older
than you, josuke higashikata.
( Josuke gasps )
Sorry about yesterday.
So, uh, that fire was crazy,
wasn’t it?
rohan: Yes.
That was approximately
2.5 million yen
worth of furniture.
those pieces were
used in the movie
"pretty woman," you know?
Not that any of that
bothers me.
( Josuke gasps )
Rohan: What? Have a seat.
Mark my words. I’ll repay you
for yesterday’s game
one way or another.
( Rohan gasps )
Uh...
That was...
Josuke, did you see that?
There was a door to a house
in the tunnel wall.
- Someone’s inside.
- ( Josuke gasps )
( Rohan gasps )
It’s a window.
there’s a room
beyond these tunnel walls,
and, from what I can see,
someone’s living in it!
there’s a man, too,
but I can’t see their faces!
What is he attempting to do?
( Gasping )
Josuke! Tell me you saw that!
Josuke: Enough!
I’ve had it with you!
Don’t think you can
screw with me forever!
( Driver gasps )
Rohan: No one else
can see the room.
Is that house a new stand user?
The man who cut off
that woman’s hand,
could he be yoshikage Kira?
Josuke: You expect me to believe
there was a room
inside the tunnel?!
You’re not fooling anyone.
is that half-baked lie
your way of getting back at me?
Rohan: So you have
no faith in me.
Is that what you’re saying?
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Rohan: That’s rich
coming from a cheater
like you.
And not only are you a cheater.
You’re a cheater who lies
to cover his tracks.
You have the gall
to accuse me of lying?
Well, I should have known
we would never see eye to eye.
You wouldn’t understand,
even if I took you
back there to see it.
Right. Let’s do this.
♪
( Gasps )
The exit.
There’s nothing here.
I could have sworn
there was something,
but it’s just a wall.
So it was an illusion.
Eh? What?!
( Groans )
( Gasps )
Wait. This is...
It’s the room
I saw from the bus.
It just appeared
out of thin air.
But what happened to the man
and woman who were in here?
- ( Rustling )
- ( Gasps )
( Thumping )
( Rohan gasps )
♪
Blast it. Something’s in there.
This room is a trap,
and I fell for it!
( Thumping )
Whatever’s in there’s
getting closer!
I don’t see a thing,
but something is coming!
- ( Gasps )
- ( Engine roars )
That wouldn’t have ended well.
It was totally invisible,
but something
was moving toward me,
something nonhuman.
That room was bait,
and the Kira-looking fellow
was an illusion.
There’s no doubt in my mind
that room is a stand.
Going it alone is risky.
I should tell Mr. Joestar.
- ( Running footsteps )
- ( Gasps )
Damn it! It’s still coming!
What the hell?! They--
they look just like
living footprints!
Are they the stand?
( Gasps ) How are they so fast?!
I got away.
So it can’t run faster
than 60 kilometers per hour.
It’s a long-range stand.
- ( Truck horn honking )
- eh?
What? It caught up to me!
But I only lowered my speed
by a fraction.
Aw, shit.
i’ll make it a book and
take control with heaven’s door!
( Gags )
No. It’s sapping my strength.
♪
Josuke: I was hoping
i’d never have to see
rohan’s smug face again,
but here I am.
He may think i’m a dumb liar,
but he’ll see
that I have a heart, too.
Now where the heck is that guy?
What?!
( Crash )
Is that rohan’s motorcycle?
Why’d it just fly
out of the tunnel?
And where’s Rohan?!
( Rohan groaning )
It’s a monster.
Highway go go:
Utterly delectable.
You shall become my nourishment!
( Rohan groans ) Heaven’s door!
Heaven’s door: This stand’s name
is highway go go.
That room was his trap.
it hunts down
anyone who enters the room.
Then it pursues them
like a rabid dog.
When it finally catches them,
it drains them
of all their nutrients.
If highway go go is able
to touch you, its weakness...
Rohan: Disappears?!
That’s crazy!
I-it’s no use.
My strength is fading.
I can’t even read.
he’s depleting
more and more of my strength.
Writing in a command
is impossible now.
Heaven’s door: What now?
Josuke: Rohan!
( Rohan gasps )
Josuke: Hey! Rohan, you here?!
rohan: Josuke.
You actually came back.
highway go go:
You have a friend. How nice.
Rohan, I believe he said.
( Rohan gasps )
♪
Josuke: Hey, Rohan,
answer me! Come on!
Rohan!
( Gasps )
Wait. Is that...
What the--Rohan!
Highway go go: Well, go ahead.
Call your friend over
so he can rescue you.
Josuke: What in the world’s
going on, Rohan?
highway go go:
Shout out for help. Do it.
There’s nothing stopping you.
i’ve left a fraction
of your body’s nutrients behind.
If you agree to call out
for his assistance,
I might be kind enough
to spare your life.
I’ll simply go after him
instead of sucking you dry.
Now, then, why don’t you
make this easy for everyone
and lure him into the room?
( Rohan panting )
highway go go:
You want to live, don’t you?
all you need to do
is get him to walk inside.
Josuke: What the hell
is this place?
If I didn’t know any better,
i’d say someone lives here.
Highway go go: Hurry, and open
your mouth before it’s too late.
If you don’t act now,
he’s likely to walk away.
It’s not as if you two actually
care about each other, right?
last chance.
Ask him to save you.
Maybe you want to die.
Rohan: If--
if I bait him into coming,
if I hand him over to you,
will--will you really keep
your promise and spare my life?
I need to hear you
say the words.
( Highway go go laughs )
But of course
I give you my word.
If you hold up your end
of our arrangement,
no harm will come to you.
Now speak.
Bring me my meal.
Rohan: Sorry, but I refuse.
- Highway go go: What?!
- Rohan: You should know
that one of Rohan kishibe’s
favorite pastimes
is saying no to fools
who think they’re tough shit,
so i’m afraid
your meal’s been cancelled.
- Josuke, run!
- ( Josuke gasps )
Rohan: No matter what happens,
you can’t come in this room!
If you do, you’re dead!
( Josuke gasps )
( Highway go go groans )
you bastard!
( Rohan chuckles )
♪
josuke: You really
don’t know me at all, do you?
I’m not one to sit back
and do as i’m told.
Now let me at this dick-wad!
His ass is grass!
Tell me where he’s hiding,
and i’ll get to work.
Rohan: What? Didn’t you
hear a single word I said?
You have to escape!
I just told you he’s deadly.
You always do the exact opposite
of what i’m thinking.
That’s why I despise you
with a burning passion.
that’s why you
bug the shit out of me!
He’s going to attack you, fool!
You’ve already let him
grab hold of your scent!
( Josuke groans )
Highway go go: At last!
time to eat!
Rohan: Heaven’s door!
( Josuke screams )
Rohan: Josuke, highway go go
will follow you anywhere
at a speed
of 60 kilometers per hour!
You have to find the user!
your only way
out of this predicament
is to defeat the thing’s user!
highway go go:
You just don’t shut up, do you?
It’s a bad habit.
( Josuke gasps ) Rohan!
( Groans )
I can’t believe it.
Rohan went out of his way
to save me.
It’s weird. I’m getting
all choked up over it.
The guy’s all right.
♪
Leave it to me, Rohan.
You said all I had to do
was find its user,
but i’ll do much more than that.
I’m gonna pummel
his soul-sucking ass.
Hang in there, Rohan!
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪