Jotaro: There it is.
The old man’s ship
is right on schedule.
He’s just about 20 minutes away.
Koichi: So, as far as you know,
mr. Joestar’s
the only passenger on board?
jotaro: He is.
The rest of the crew members
are from
the speedwagon foundation.
Even so, i’m sure chili pepper
will try to pass over the water
and sneak
onto the old man’s ship,
despite the fact
that he’s confined
to areas with electricity.
If he gets to Joseph first,
he’ll kill him
without a second thought,
and everything
we’ve gone through
will have been for nothing.
Okuyasu: Hey, jotaro,
we checked the boat over,
and it’s good to go!
Josuke: We also
checked the battery.
There’s no sign of him in here.
We’re ready to set out
whenever you give the word.
Jotaro: About that,
only okuyasu and I
are heading over
to meet with the old man.
- Koichi: Huh?
- Okuyasu: Eh?
Jotaro: I want you to stay here
and hold down the fort
with koichi.
Koichi: Stay here? But you’ll
need backup, won’t you?
Josuke: Yeah, he’s right!
Jotaro: Josuke,
chili pepper’s user
is hiding
somewhere in this harbor,
watching our every move.
understand?
( Both gasp )
jotaro:
He’s laying low right now
and waiting for us
to do something
that’ll give away
the ship’s position...
And my gut’s telling me a boat
won’t be his hiding place.
All he needs to make it over
to the old man is a battery
and something faster
than a speedboat.
once he puts
those two things together,
he’ll use it
to send chili pepper
flying to the old man’s ship.
Koichi: Wait a second!
are you thinking
he’s gonna take to the sky?
jotaro: Yeah.
To be perfectly frank,
he’s probably making off
with a remote-controlled plane
as we speak.
Koichi: That thought
hadn’t even occurred to me!
But it’s possible.
Once they pick up speed,
model airplanes can fly
over 100 kilometers per hour,
faster than the motorboat’s
top speed!
And because chili pepper’ll
be in control of it,
he can fly the plane
as far and as high
as the battery will take him!
he doesn’t need
a remote-control’s signal!
Jotaro: Listen, josuke,
if you spot anything
flying around here, I want you
to search for the user.
Koichi’s reverb has
a range of 50 meters,
- so he can help out, too.
- ( Koichi grunts )
jotaro: If that stand
gets to the ship before we do,
the old man is as good as dead.
Your job is to stay on watch
and protect your father
from the harbor.
We clear, josuke?
Josuke: Yeah.
From here on out,
we don’t have
a single second to spare.
Joestar’s life is on the line.
♪
Koichi: Best of luck, okuyasu.
Okuyasu: Huh?
( Grunts )
Same to you, koichi.
♪
Sailor: In about 20 minutes,
we’ll finally arrive at the port
of morioh, Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: Is that right?
Uh...
I seem to have
misplaced my cane.
- ( Hand clanking )
- Have you seen it?
Sailor: Uh, isn’t that it
right in front of you, sir?
Joseph: Ah.
( Grunting )
Josuke: So he’s my father, huh?
( Koichi gasps )
Josuke, are you all right?
Josuke: I’m just processing.
Never met this guy in my life,
yet i’m supposed to accept
that he’s my father.
I don’t know. It’s...
( Sighs ) But the only thing
that matters right now
is his life is in danger.
If I didn’t even lift a finger
to help, i’d always regret it.
Besides, my mom would fall apart
if the guy croaked.
( Chili pepper growls )
Damn that jotaro!
if he left
you two mouth-breathers behind
- to sniff out my user...
- ( Koichi gasps )
Chili pepper: That means
he completely saw through
my remote-controlled
plane trick.
Josuke: There you are,
chili pepper!
Chili pepper: Yah!
( Koichi gasps )
User: I’ll give this
to jotaro kujo.
The man’s sharp as a tack.
He’s the last person
i’d want finding me.
He’d just kill my vibe.
Speaking of killing, this
remote-controlled spitfire plane
can reach Joseph joestar’s boat
in a mere five minutes.
A dinged-up, old motorboat,
on the other hand,
would take about eight to ten.
Meaning, if I can
put you two down
for a dirt nap in three minutes,
it’ll give me time
to catch up and pass ’em.
josuke: Wait!
Are you trying to tell me
you’re chili pepper’s user?!
Akira: You’re looking
at Akira otoishi,
age 19. Oh, and don’t let
the guitar throw you off.
♪
One day, I wanna be
a rocking guitarist
the likes of Jimi Hendrix
and Jeff Beck.
That’s why I keep this sweet
little mama on my person
24 hours a day,
seven days a week.
One day, the masses will look up
from their mundane lives, and
they’ll be lining up for miles
to let my music
knock them off their feet.
( Crowd cheering )
People around the world
will know my name.
Oh, yeah.
Koichi: T-this can’t be good.
I never thought a stand user
would come out of hiding,
which means there’s
no doubt in his mind
that he can slaughter both me
and josuke without much trouble!
( Akira chuckles )
Chili pepper: I’m ready for
round two with shining diamond,
but i’ll only use
my little pinkie,
just like I did with okuyasu.
Josuke: You should
get back, koichi.
( Akira chuckles )
It’s game on,
josuke higashikata!
- Josuke: Just a minute.
- Akira: Huh?
Josuke: If you’re
planning to use
only your pinkie
in this showdown,
then i’ve got
a couple of rules of my own.
Akira: You can take your rules
and shove ’em, fool!
Rules are wasted
on a punk kid like you!
Eh? ( Shrieks )
You damn bastard!
How dare you?!
Josuke: Well, you did say
that rules are wasted on me.
You also said something
about bringing me down
with your pinkie finger.
So what’s the wannabe rocker
otoishi gonna do now?
Akira: I’ll kill you.
Josuke: You already said that!
don’t you have
any new material, fool?!
( Akira groaning )
The pain in my finger
is unbearable.
I have to redirect it
onto something. ( Groans )
This gnawing rage,
I have to vent to someone!
( Groaning )
- ( Bone cracks )
- ( Screams )
♪
( Koichi gasps )
Awesome.
Akira: First, i’ll kill you!
Then the old gasbag!
after that,
your precious mommies!
( Josuke gasps )
akira: Ahh.
That was pure ecstasy.
My heart is free again.
There’s no greater euphoria
than letting
your blistering rage fly.
Josuke: Let’s test
that theory, otoishi!
( Shining diamond yells )
♪
- What the hell?! How’d he...
- ( Akira chuckles )
josuke: I know stands
can move at incredible speeds,
but this is different.
It’s like he found a way
to teleport behind me.
Koichi: No, josuke,
that’s not what happened.
I was able to see everything
back there.
Otoishi didn’t take
a single step.
You’re the one
who changed position.
- Something moved you!
- Josuke: Say what?
Koichi: Chili pepper
suddenly appeared
and flipped shining diamond
around 180 degrees
without you
even realizing it.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Koichi: Just look.
You’re facing the ocean.
Josuke: Chili pepper did that?
Where is he now, koichi?
I don’t see that sparky bastard.
Koichi: He’s hiding underground.
He’s using the storm drains
to come and go!
He popped halfway out of
the drain to turn you around!
There must be underground
electrical lines
running all over the place!
Akira: A little soul-searching
always gives me the boost I need
to bring the pain.
Koichi: Behind you!
On your right!
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Shining diamond: Dora!
Dora!
Koichi: He’s right behind you!
( Shining diamond yells )
( Chili pepper laughs )
Koichi: He bolts back
into the electrical wires
at the last second,
and his speed
makes him hard to pin down!
Jotaro’s the only one
who can keep up with him.
What are we gonna do?!
Akira: Here in the harbor,
you don’t have the luxury
of digging up asphalt
and severing all the wires,
josuke higashikata.
However, the bigger the opening
you make in the ground
with shining diamond,
the easier it is
to surface from below
and knock your lights out!
Koichi: Josuke,
he’s on your right!
No, in front!
Behind you!
No, wait! He’s--
( gasping )
this is like a game
of whack-a-mole on steroids!
I can’t follow his movements at
all when he’s going that fast!
( Shining diamond yelling )
chili pepper:
What’s the matter, josuke?
Can’t keep your eye
on the birdie?!
- ( Koichi whimpering )
- ( Blows smacking )
Josuke, no!
Akira: Well, look at that.
Two minutes to spare.
That gives me plenty of time
to finish this.
( Josuke panting )
Hey, koichi, keep track
of chili pepper’s location,
and call it out to me.
at this range,
he’s moving too fast
for my eyes to follow.
Koichi: But if you can’t follow
him, how am I supposed to?
As soon as I find him,
he disappears!
Josuke: Then you have
to look harder, koichi.
We’re about to win this,
and by now, you should know
what i’m thinking.
( Koichi gasps ) I should?
( Gasps )
That muck on the ground.
The asphalt’s turned into tar,
and the drains are covered
in all the oil from the tar.
i get it now.
When josuke struck the ground,
he reduced the asphalt
to its most basic ingredients,
which means...
Behind you, on the left!
( Shining diamond yelling )
( Akira groans )
Koichi: Oh, yeah!
Right in the kisser!
Josuke: Well, that’s great.
our strategy
worked like a charm.
Guess i’m the superstar now,
’cause i’m gonna rock
this loser’s world.
Okuyasu: Huh?
It’s the boat!
She’s dead ahead, jotaro!
See? We’re almost there!
Jotaro: Don’t drop
your guard yet.
Okuyasu: Huh? Whoa!
What the hell’s
happenin’ over there?!
Josuke! Koichi!
♪
Koichi: What’s that light?
Akira: I underestimated you,
josuke higashikata.
I was too focused
on my presentation
and should have
just gone in for the kill.
But i’ve learned my lesson.
The juvenile me is no more.
i’m reborn
as a killing machine!
And for my first act of anarchy,
i’ll focus all of morioh’s
electricity into chili pepper.
chili pepper:
This is my last resort.
Using this technique
means temporarily
knocking out power
all over town,
which i’m forced to draw on
for my lifeblood!
But none of that matters now.
After i’ve done away
with you cretins,
i’ll bolt over
to the r.C. Plane’s battery!
Then i’ll fly over to Joseph
and slit his throat!
Koichi: What the--
I can’t see a thing!
( Josuke groans )
Bastard.
- ( Shining diamond yelling )
- Chili pepper: Hah!
Ya-hah!
( Josuke gags )
( Koichi wails )
I don’t believe it!
chili pepper
got the best of josuke!
( Josuke gags )
Koichi: Josuke!
( Akira laughs )
( Josuke groans )
chili pepper:
Is it sinking in yet?
This entire town’s electrical
power is at my disposal.
Akira: And to really
drive the point home,
i’ll be sure to charge
my electric bill for the month
- to your address. ( Chuckles )
- ( Josuke growls )
chili pepper:
It’s lights out, josuke!
Huh? ( Grunting )
( Akira gasps )
Is that a tire?!
Josuke: Just as I expected,
you were too dense
to figure it out.
Akira: Huh?
Now I understand!
You blew up that tire
on purpose!
It was all part of your plan
to entomb my stand in rubber!
Koichi: Of course!
Rubber is an insulator,
so it doesn’t
conduct electricity!
chili pepper
is powerless in there!
Chili pepper: Damn it all!
Koichi: All right! We just
have to wait for jotaro now.
- Akira: Just kidding.
- koichi: Eh?
akira: A good idea,
but that’s not gonna work on me.
Hah! Your plan
might have succeeded
had the rubber
been a meter thick,
but this flimsy excuse
for a trap
doesn’t even register
as a threat.
So let me show you
some real power.
- Dumb-ass!
- ( Koichi gasps )
( Akira laughs )
You’ve lost this battle, josuke!
( Laughs )
Josuke: Just great.
you really are
as stupid as you look.
Having your stand
break through the tire
was the dumbest thing
you could have done.
- Chili pepper: Huh? ( Yells )
- Akira: Huh?!
Chili pepper: I forgot
about the air in the tire!
Koichi: The pressure release
launched him like a rocket!
Chili pepper: No, not the ocean!
Anything but the ocean!
Koichi: Oh, yeah, that’s right.
Salt water conducts electricity,
and in the ocean,
the electricity that powers him
will scatter in every direction.
chili pepper:
I’m sorry I tried to kill you!
Please, just get me
out of here!
josuke: Didn’t you
say something about getting rid
of your juvenile self
a while back?
Sorry. That’s impossible
for a lowlife like you.
( Chili pepper grunting )
I’m...dissolving.
Koichi: His stand’s
been completely diffused,
which means that Akira is...
( Sizzling )
Is--is he dead?
Reverb: Jotaro!
I have some great news.
it wasn’t easy,
but we managed to defeat
chili pepper’s user.
jotaro: Nice job.
We can breathe easier now.
Okuyasu: So this old geezer
is josuke’s dad, huh?
He’s kinda buff,
but at the same time,
it looks like he’s got
one foot in the grave.
joseph: You,
I don’t believe we’ve met.
Don’t just stand there.
Introduce yourself.
Okuyasu: I’m okuyasu, sir.
Joseph: Okuyasu?
okuyasu: I live
in josuke’s neighborhood,
and i’m also a stand user.
- Joseph: Hmm?
- Okuyasu: I’m a stand user!
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Okuyasu growls )
I said i’m a stand user!
joseph: Ah.
You’re a secondhand computer?
Okuyasu: I’m a stand user!
Joseph: Oh, a stand user.
you young folks
should really learn to speak up
and quit mumbling.
by the way, osomatsu,
I can’t seem to find my cane.
You wouldn’t happen to know
where I left it, would you?
( Okuyasu groans )
Joseph: Oops, silly me.
I’m holding the damn thing
right here in my hand.
Okuyasu: Has he
lost his marbles?
Man: Mr. Joestar.
I’ve come to pick up
your luggage, sir.
Okuyasu: Huh?
Joseph: If it wouldn’t
be too much trouble,
would you mind
answering a question?
has josuke
ever mentioned me to you,
the man who went 16 years
without knowing he had a son
out there who needed him?
has he said
anything about me at all?
Okuyasu: Hmm. I hate to say it,
but, no, he hasn’t
said much about you.
Joseph: Is that so?
Well, I guess it’s
to be expected. ( Sighs )
( Josuke sighs )
Koichi: All right!
They’re finally here!
Look, josuke. Do you see ’em?
Josuke: Yeah. Cool, I guess.
- koichi: Huh?
- Josuke: If i’m being honest,
I kinda wish he’d just go home
and leave us in peace.
Koichi: Josuke.
Josuke: It’s the truth,
but don’t get me wrong.
I’m glad otoishi
didn’t kill him.
Now we can go back to our lives.
Well, some of us.
I’ve never laid eyes
on the guy before.
how am I supposed
to think of him as my dad?
He’s barely a stranger.
Just watch. It’s gonna be
awkward for us both.
( Koichi sighs )
Josuke: It’s not like
I hate him or anything,
but I have to think
about my mom’s well-being, too.
You get where i’m coming from,
right? Koichi?
- Koichi: No. It can’t be.
- Josuke: Eh?
Koichi: Josuke, look over there!
H-his body’s gone!
♪
Jotaro, we’ve got trouble!
Akira otoishi’s body
disappeared!
( Jotaro gasps )
Koichi: He’s still alive!
What are we gonna do?!
Sailor: Red alert!
We’ve been boarded by the enemy!
akira otoishi
is somehow still alive!
Okuyasu: Are you kidding me?
Sailor: Take Mr. Joes--
- ( gasps )
- ( Akira gasps )
Sailor: Who are you?
okuyasu:
Hey, did you say something?
Sailor: No. He, uh...
Akira: I’m the one who said it!
I was trying to tell you
that he’s not
from the speedwagon foundation!
Sailor: What the hell
are you talking about?!
He’s the enemy!
Okuyasu: So you’re the guy
I have to kill!
sailor: Wait!
I’m on your side here!
i’m the one
who told you about the enemy
in the first place, remember?
Would the real enemy
do something like that?!
He’s the one you wanna beat up!
Okuyasu: Yeah, that makes sense.
Akira: Surely you
haven’t forgotten
i’m the one
who pointed out the enemy!
This poser came here to throw
you off your guard!
- Don’t fall for it!
- Okuyasu: Wait.
You’re makin’ sense, too.
Then the question is,
who’s the user?
- Both: He’s the user!
- Okuyasu: Damn it!
Why do I have to make
another important decision?
This is what I get
for relying on my bro
for everything all these years.
Akira: Bumping off okuyasu
will be easy enough,
and thankfully jotaro
hasn’t seen my face yet.
I just have to kill Joseph
and get the hell out of dodge.
It’ll be easy! These
halfwits’ll never catch me!
Okuyasu: It’s chili pepper!
That’s not good.
Joseph: Huh? You said
you got me a smelly sweater?
No, thanks!
Akira: Time to die!
( Okuyasu groaning )
( Akira growls )
Okuyasu: I figured it out.
The stand user...
Has to be you!
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Chili pepper screams )
Okuyasu: Nobody fools me twice.
Don’t ever forget that,
you dumb-ass!
Akira: You figured out
I was the user. How?
Okuyasu: It was easy.
Akira: Tell me already.
Okuyasu: I was gonna beat
the shit out of both of you
and sort it out later!
That deduction stuff
is for the birds!
( Koichi laughs )
♪
- Joseph: Eh?
- Koichi: Huh?
( Joseph sighs )
Ohh! ( Gasps )
( Koichi gasps )
Josuke: You should be careful.
One misstep, and you’ll
be going for an unwanted swim.
Joseph: Right. Sorry.
if I had my cane,
I could manage by myself,
but it broke a few moments ago.
It was the strangest thing.
Josuke: Then, I don’t
have much of a choice.
Here. You can hold on to me.
( Josuke gasping )
( Koichi chuckles )
( Laughs )
okuyasu: Huh?
Hey, I just had a great idea.
Josuke should have his
shining diamond fix the cane.
Koichi: Do you even
hear yourself, okuyasu?
Sometimes it’s like
you don’t have a brain.
Okuyasu: It is? But why?
Koichi: Come on.
Isn’t it obvious?
just this once,
it’s better to leave it broken.
Okuyasu: But why?
Seriously.
Jotaro: Now, if we can retrieve
the bow and arrow,
it’ll all be over,
and this town
will be safe again.
♪
( Handle squeaks )
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪