♪
Yoshihiro: Oh, yoshikage,
my darling boy, where are you?
i’ve looked all over
and can’t find you anywhere.
You must have been forced
to change your face and name
and go into hiding.
My heart aches for you,
my poor son.
I’ll make sure they pay dearly.
Jotaro: You got that?
We need to look further
into the recent
missing-person cases.
That includes runaways.
joseph: Hang on.
Didn’t Kira go into hiding?
You really think
he’d risk capture
by continuing
his murdering spree?
Jotaro: He won’t be
able to brush aside
his murderous impulses.
that’s just
how serial killers work.
He will kill again.
( Joseph grumbles )
Koichi: I wonder if just waiting
for something to happen
is the best way to go?
In all this time,
we still haven’t found
a single clue
leading us to Kira.
Josuke: Well, it’s been
bothering me a lot, too,
but you guys remember
what jotaro said, don’t you?
As soon as he finds something,
we spring to action.
According to him,
we should go back
to being ordinary students
until then.
I’d rather hunt down
that bastard Kira
than go back
to hitting the books.
We almost got him before, so I
bet the next time we see him,
it’ll be a one-two knockout!
( Grunts )
Rohan: Yes. And since i’m
repairing the fire damage,
i’d like to have
some renovations done, too.
Yoshihiro: That little punk!
He’s snapping pictures of people
in search of my son!
Rohan: Now would you mind
giving me an estimate?
Yoshihiro: Jotaro and his
insufferable stand-user posse
think they’re so smart.
I’ll annihilate these parasites,
and the best way to do that
is by creating new stand users.
Huh? Wait a minute!
Whuhh!
No doubt about it.
Altered appearance or not,
the bond of a father and son
can’t be broken.
I could never mistake
my son for another.
i’ve found you
at last, yoshikage--huh?
♪
Hayato: Just you wait.
I’ll find out who you
really are, imposter.
yoshihiro:
You have to be kidding me! Uhh!
If that brat uncovers
my son’s secret,
the stand users
will sniff him out.
enough’s enough.
I have to put an end to this!
I’ll protect yoshikage
with every fiber of my being!
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
♪
Koichi: See you later!
i’m gonna be late,
and i’m class monitor today!
( Footsteps shuffling )
( Josuke yawns )
I stayed up way too late.
i’m exhausted.
Okuyasu: Man,
that sucks for you.
I slept like a rock, so i’m
feeling as fit as a fiddle.
( Gasps )
- Check it out, josuke.
- josuke: Hmm?
Okuyasu: Some random binoculars.
Somebody must have
left them behind.
josuke: Wow,
it doesn’t take much
to pique your interest,
does it, buddy?
Don’t pick them up.
That’s gross.
Okuyasu: What? You think?
Mikitaka: I can assure you
I am not gross!
( Both yell )
Mikitaka: Hello,
josuke and okuyasu.
Josuke: Oh, it’s you again!
Don’t scare us
like that, mikitaka.
Okuyasu: No kiddin’!
My heart isn’t built
for that kind of shock!
mikitaka: Oh,
you’re being too kind.
Josuke: That wasn’t
a compliment, you know.
Okuyasu: Oh, yeah, that’s right.
You’ve got perfect timing.
It’s high time for you
to come clean about something,
Mr. Alien man.
You’re not actually
from outer space, are you?
you’re just
a run-of-the-mill stand user
who believes he’s an alien
for some reason.
spill the beans!
All this lyin’ ain’t cool!
Mikitaka: What do you mean?
I have no beans,
- and I really am an alien.
- Okuyasu: There you go,
talkin’ like
a frickin’ weirdo again!
josuke: So, uh,
here’s a question for you.
Why were you lying out here
as a pair of binoculars?
It’s a little weird.
mikitaka: Well, I wanted
the two of you to see something,
hence my waiting
here in the open.
Okuyasu: That?
Mikitaka: Yes.
It’s a transmission tower,
to be exact.
Okuyasu: Huh. You don’t say.
Josuke: Uh, calling it that
might be a bit of a stretch.
Without any of its power lines,
it’s more
of a relic of the past.
When redevelopment
took over here,
most of the excess power lines
were taken down
and moved underground.
Okuyasu: Why did you want us
to see that old thing?
Josuke: Is that
what you’re using
to communicate
with life on other planets?
Mikitaka: Unless i’m mistaken,
there’s smoke
wafting up from around
the center of the tower.
Both: Hmm?
Okuyasu: Whoa! You’re right!
Josuke: Yeah. How weird!
Mikitaka: Please use me
to take a closer look.
♪
Josuke: What the--
there’s a kettle!
Okuyasu: Seriously?!
But how is that possible?!
That tower is, like,
20 meters in the air!
Mikitaka: Indeed, but aim me
about five meters higher.
Both: Huh?
Josuke: You don’t
see that every day.
Okuyasu: Stop hogging the alien!
I wanna see!
Ahh!
Oh, wow! It’s a dude!
There’s a guy sitting up there,
cooking some grub!
Josuke: What?! Let me see!
Okuyasu: I think that tower
might be his home.
And he looks comfy,
so he’s probably spent
his entire life up there!
He can fish from the river,
and he’s got cucumbers growing!
Nice! That’s impressive!
Josuke: I have
to agree with you.
It’s like this guy is living
in one of those fancy,
self-sufficient homes.
mikitaka:
This world has no shortages
of curious individuals.
( Josuke gasps )
( Man gasping )
Josuke: Look out!
( Metal rings )
Okuyasu: Did you see that?
Josuke: This guy has to be
a new stand user.
Okuyasu: He just flew
right through the air
like it was nothing!
josuke: Yeah, I know,
but what’s a stand user doing
living on a transmission tower?
Mikitaka: If we want to find out
the answer to that,
I believe we’ll need
to take a closer look.
Man: What do you know?
They’ve arrived at last.
I wonder what I did to finally
catch their curious eyes?
come on over.
It’s been quite a while
since i’ve indulged
in a little chitchat.
Okuyasu: Check it out.
Looks like that tower dude
might have noticed
that we noticed him.
You wanna get closer?
josuke: Oh, yeah,
but we have to play it safe.
we still don’t know
if that user is on our side
or if he’s angling
to take us out.
( Koichi panting )
( Gasps ) Huh?
Is there something
I can do for you?
Sorry to be rude,
but i’m kinda in--
( gasps )
( Both gasp )
Okuyasu: This thing
looks a lot bigger
once you get up close to it.
Man: If you fellas
know what’s good for you,
you’ll stop right there
and won’t get any closer!
didn’t you two
hear what I said? Get back!
I just answered
the call of nature,
and, trust me, you don’t wanna
be there to get the message.
Both: Huh?
Josuke: I’m really
not following.
Okuyasu: What the hell?!
- This is disgusting!
- ( Both yell )
Man: Don’t say
I didn’t warn you.
i needed
to fertilize the garden.
Josuke: Guh! That’s so gross!
Man: Watch your mouth!
That’s impolite!
I designed this nifty
contraption so it would
distribute the fertilizer
to all the plants below!
I’m all about that zero-waste
lifestyle, you know.
on the right
are asiatic dayflowers,
mountain asparagus,
and watercress.
They’re all completely edible!
and with all
of these plants around,
catching nibbling rabbits
is a cinch,
so i’ve got the best
of both worlds, baby!
Josuke: No way! So you’re really
living up there all alone?
Doesn’t this tower belong
to some electric company?
Man: What are you talking about?
I paid for this house with
my own money. It’s all mine.
I bought this abandoned tower
for 100,000 yen
and transformed it into
my self-sufficient dream house.
Okuyasu: You bought it?
Josuke: For 100,000 yen?
Man: Yes, that’s right.
it was a steal.
Since I support myself,
i’m not stuck working
for some lame company.
It’s a pretty sweet life,
if you think about it.
I don’t have to leave the house,
and I get all the exercise
I could ever need. Heh.
I mean, do you see this view?
It’s spectacular.
josuke: Wait!
Run that by me again.
You don’t even have to leave?
Just how long have you
been living up there, anyway?
Man: I suppose i’ve been here
for about three years now.
- Okuyasu: What?!
- Josuke: Three years?!
Man: I probably haven’t touched
terra firma in nearly a month.
Okuyasu: What are
we gonna do, josuke?
I had no idea such an idiot
was living right
under our noses in morioh.
if you ask me,
he’s a pure-grade nut case!
He’s just living out a fantasy,
but there’s no way he’d be
dumb enough to attack us.
Josuke: You’re right.
For now, at least,
our best option is heading back
and reporting to jotaro.
Then again...
Something just doesn’t
feel right about this.
♪
Rohan: Hmm.
Eh?
What is he doing there?
How strange.
I suppose children
like to take videos
like anyone else.
But why is he hiding
behind that pillar?
It’s almost as if he’s
up to the same thing I am.
He’s following someone and
capturing their every move.
could his target
be someone in this picture?
Hmm?
"Hayato kawajiri," huh?
There’s something’s very unusual
about this kid.
♪
Tomoko: Hey, i’m home! Huh?
Is that boy still here?
hey, josuke,
it’s time for school.
Haven’t you left yet?
Josuke!
( Sighs )
I could go for some food.
Hmm? ( Gasps )
( Groans )
He did not.
that little shit
only thinks about himself.
He takes a giant bite out
of my favorite kamakura custar
and pops it back in the fridge
like it never happened?!
And there were two in here.
Where’s the other one?
Hmph. Man, that kid
pisses me off sometimes.
♪
Both: Hmm?
Josuke: Hey, look sharp!
Something fell
out of your pocket!
Hey, is that a photo?
Man: Would you two
mind skedaddling?
And don’t worry about
picking that picture up.
I’ll get it later.
Josuke: It looks like
an ordinary polaroid to me.
Why’s he so freaked out?
Man: It’s fine! Just leave!
Josuke: What?! You’re...
okuyasu: Hey!
What’s goin’ on, josuke?
Josuke: At last!
You’re kira’s old man!
I should have known your
crusty ass was behind all this!
Man: I’ve been waiting
for this moment.
- You’ve stepped into my abode.
- ( Both gasp )
Man: If you tell
someone to come in,
they chicken out and refuse,
but if you
tell them the opposite,
they get pissed and enter.
You’ve at long last entered
into superfly,
josuke higashikata!
Josuke: Wait. I’ve what?
Yoshihiro: Well done,
toyohiro kanedaichi!
You lured him in
hook, line, and sinker!
Now our friend josuke
has a new home!
Kudos, my friend!
Okuyasu: That sounds bad, bro!
You gotta come back!
Get moving, josuke!
Josuke: No, we’ve finally
found kira’s dad,
and he’s got the arrow!
( Yoshihiro laughs )
Josuke: No! Get back here!
Eh?
( Okuyasu gasps )
Toyohiro: I’m sure
you’re confused,
so let me explain.
Once someone steps
into the tower’s realm,
it won’t spit them out
until its next victim steps in.
However, if they try
to force their way out,
they simply become
part of the tower.
That’s the secret ability
of my stand, superfly!
Yoshihiro: We’ve got you now,
josuke higashikata!
make sure he stays
nice and comfy now, toyohiro!
( Laughs )
( Josuke gasping )
Okuyasu: Josuke!
Josuke: Damn it all.
( Grunts )
Eh?
Toyohiro: I have a bit
of a confession to make.
Superfly is indeed my stand,
but it isn’t exactly
under my control.
It pretty much does
whatever it wants,
and now that you’re here,
i can take off.
I’ve been trapped by superfly
for the entirety
of my stay here.
Well, take care of her for me.
- I’ve got a life to enjoy.
- ( Josuke growls )
okuyasu: So the sly
son of a bitch is in cahoots
with that grandpa ghost dude
from the picture.
Mikitaka: Mr. Okuyasu,
is there any way
I could possibly be
of assistance to you?
Okuyasu: You’ll just get hurt,
so stay out of it.
Your assistance
is no longer needed.
Now, if you could
change your body
into some sticks of dynamite
instead of dice or binoculars,
we might have
something to work with.
mikitaka: Oh,
that would be impossible.
I can’t change into any object
stronger than myself,
so explosives and
large mechanisms are off limits.
Perhaps there’s another way
I can be of use.
Okuyasu: Oh, shut up!
I already told you
there’s not a damn thing
you can do.
get out of here,
and let us do what we do best.
that asshole thinks i’m
just gonna let him trap his prey
and make some super-cool escape.
But he’s about to find out
he messed
with the wrong stand users.
josuke: Hey.
You gonna go for it, okuyasu?
Okuyasu: I’m ready to go
when you are, buddy.
This rusty tower
has got nothing on us.
Let’s bring it down, josuke!
Josuke: Heh. Right!
busting outta here
is gonna be a snap and a half.
( All yell )
Toyohiro: Whoa there!
What are you doing?
Damn these dicks!
How the hell did
they get so strong?!
Okuyasu: This thing’s
pretty frickin’ solid,
but if we keep pounding it
like we have been,
it’ll snap in two
and fall over in no time.
See for yourself!
You’re about to come
crashing down
to good old terra firma!
Toyohiro: You dumbass! Do you
think you two can scare me?
I had a feeling you’d go
straight to using your fists.
looks like
you haven’t noticed yet.
This tower has absorbed
the power of your attacks
and has redistributed the force
over its entire structure.
okuyasu: Huh? What’s
this jackass babbling about?
Hang tight! You’ll be
out of this metal deathtrap
before you know it!
here we go!
Josuke: Hold it, okuyasu.
listen for a sec.
Okuyasu: Huh?
( Tower vibrating )
josuke: I’m getting
a real bad feeling about this.
that sound.
What the hell is he planning?
Toyohiro: What you’re
hearing is the sound
of the energy
left over from your punches
reverberating
throughout the whole tower.
Josuke: What?
Toyohiro: Mind if I ask
you boys a question?
Have either of you ever heard
of the law of conservation?
Once energy has been collected,
it’ll eventually be released
for use in a different form,
and I wonder
where it’s gonna go now.
Josuke: Oh, shit.
- Okuyasu, get down!
- Okuyasu: Huh?
Josuke: What?!
Whuhh!
Toyohiro: Punch the tower
as much as you’d like.
All the energy you two idiots
are putting out
is just going
to go around and around
and come right back
to bite you in the ass.
so go ahead!
You’re only hurting yourselves!
Why not save the money
in hospital bills
and accept
that you’re outmatched?
It doesn’t matter
how strong you are.
Nothing you do will be able
to destroy this tower!
( Okuyasu gasping )
Josuke: Okuyasu!
okuyasu:
I’m kinda worried, josuke.
I wasn’t quick enough
to dodge it.
One of those attacks
left a hole in my side.
Toyohiro: Guess I should have
warned you about that, huh?
I can see your thoughts racing.
you think if you
can manage to defeat me,
the user,
you’ll have a way out,
but that’s merely a pipe dream.
Remember, this stand exists
independently of me.
Even if I were to just
drop dead, that would never
stop this tower from ensnaring
victims until the end of time.
That’s superfly’s
special ability.
( Okuyasu grunting )
Josuke, i--
josuke: Until the end of time?
( Toyohiro grunts )
Don’t look so serious, josuke.
All you have to do is find
someone else to take your place.
It’s not rocket science.
One person goes in,
and one comes out.
It’s a simple exchange.
Trap some poor fool,
and get yourself out.
it’s kinda like
that card game, old maid.
It’s a lot like human society.
Just hand over the old maid
to some other fool
and get the hell out of dodge.
Don’t you agree?
Mikitaka: I do, wholeheartedly.
Pulling someone else in
will certainly help josuke.
Toyohiro: Hmm? ( Gasps )
- Okuyasu: How’d he...
- ( Josuke gasps )
mikitaka: And I think
you’re the perfect candidate.
Time to go back to the tower.
You’re grounded.
( Toyohiro yells )
Okuyasu: Eh? Holy...
Josuke: Mikitaka, you sly dog!
Toyohiro: What the hell
is going on here?!
Where did you come from,
and how are you a power line?
What sort of power is this?!
Mikitaka: How very kind
of you to ask.
I possess these powers
due to my being an alien.
- ( Toyohiro gasps )
- Okuyasu: Yeah!
You’ve got him now!
Way to be useful, alien dude!
Mikitaka: Move quickly now.
Please exit the confines
of the tower, Mr. Josuke.
Toyohiro: Damn you.
okuyasu: Thanks!
You frickin’ rock, mikitaka!
You heard him, josuke!
Get out of there!
Leave the tower
before it’s too late!
Josuke: Yeah! On my way!
♪
Sweet! I made it out!
Toyohiro: You bastard!
What even are you?!
the guy in the photo
told me about josuke’s allies,
but he never mentioned
a freak show like you!
Mikitaka: Being an alien,
I have no knowledge
of this so-called old maid game,
but I don’t like the way
you tricked josuke and tried
to trap him here forever.
it’s an awful lot
like an adult beating a child
at a new year’s card game
by cheating.
That is why I brought you back.
You don’t deserve to be free.
You’re never leaving
this tower.
( Toyohiro gasps )
( Chuckles )
Mikitaka: Hmm?
Toyohiro: Here’s the thing.
i’ve developed
these really thick calluses
from swinging around
up here all this time.
they’re so thick,
I can hide things in them.
Now die, dickhead!
Mikitaka: You seem to assume
what’s in your hand
is a part of me,
but I am afraid
that is a misconception.
What you’re holding isn’t me,
but the power line
you were hanging on to.
As you can see, I am fine.
( Toyohiro screams )
Okuyasu: Yeah, he did it!
Josuke: That was
totally epic, mikitaka!
Now get yourself to the top,
and get over here!
toyohiro:
After years of waiting,
you finally stepped
into my tower’s realm.
Do you really think
i’d let you walk away?
You’re looking at a man
who’s spent every moment
of every day thinking about
escaping this godforsaken tower!
- ( Mikitaka groans )
- ( Both gasp )
Toyohiro: Have you already
forgotten my warning?
this tower will return
any attack back to the attacker.
That wire is also
a part of this tower.
I purposely severed the line
so that the opening
would face you.
Mikitaka: I-is this really
the place where I meet my end?
- ( Groans )
- Josuke: No! Mikitaka!
Get your ass out of there!
I can heal the wound,
but you have to leave the tower!
toyohiro: Oh, no!
The only one leaving here is me!
♪
Direction and angle, check.
( Mikitaka gasps )
Toyohiro: If you strike it,
it strikes back.
Okuyasu: Mikitaka!
Josuke: You sick bastard!
Toyohiro: You definitely made
escaping a little bit tougher,
I must admit, but all of
that ugliness is behind us now.
i would wager
prying those suckers out
will sting just a touch,
but you’ll have all
the time in the world to heal.
Feel free to use the medicinal
herbs in the garden.
josuke: Bastard!
I’ll make sure you pay for that!
Even if you somehow manage
to make it out of that tower,
i’ll chase your deceitful ass
to the ends of the earth!
Toyohiro: Oh, you can try,
but you won’t succeed.
From what that old man told me,
you still haven’t even
uncovered the whereabouts
of yoshikage Kira.
( Both gasp )
( Toyohiro chuckles )
( Doorbell rings )
♪
rohan: Who is this?
I’ve never seen him before.
♪
( Fingernails rustle )
( Pencil snaps )
Hayato: I have to figure out
who that man is.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪