( Knife grinding )
♪
( Man chuckles )
( Animal growling )
Okuyasu: Man,
i’m wastin’ away over here.
After we visit my bro’s grave,
what do you say we find a place
to get somethin’ to eat?
Josuke: I’m good,
but don’t let me stop you.
( Okuyasu yawns ) Ooh?
Says here there’s
a new Italian restaurant,
and it’s just up the road.
Josuke: Wait. Isn’t that
where the cemetery is?
Not the best place
for a restaurant
or anything, for that matter.
Okuyasu: Oh, josuke,
this is just the kind
of wacky food destination that
brings people in from all over.
"Ahh. It’s to die for!
My mouth won’t stop watering!"
Or whatever it is
the foodies say!
I just wanna go. Come on,
josuke. What do you say?!
Josuke: This is it?
I thought
this building was vacant.
Okuyasu:
Maybe they remodeled it.
It sure has character.
( Chuckles )
Josuke: Huh?
That’s weird.
What’s "diner dependent" mean?
( Entry bell rings )
Okuyasu: I’m digging the vibe
this place has going on.
- ( Laughs )
- Man: Benvenuto!
♪
Two today?
Here. Please feel free
to have a seat.
Okuyasu: Oh. Don’t mind if I do.
Chef: Here you go.
Josuke: Uh, right.
Okuyasu: So, chef,
you a foreigner, or what?
Chef: Si, signore.
I am originally from Italy.
My name is tonio trendy,
but you can call me tonio.
( Okuyasu gasps )
This is the best day ever!
I finally get to eat
authentic Italian food.
Tonio: My role as a chef
has taken me to many countries.
I’ve used the flavors
of my homeland and fused them
with the best culinary
traditions in the world.
Now i’ve made my way to Japan
in search of new opportunities.
Your morioh is
such a magnificent town.
You can find several farms with
many kinds of fresh produce.
Its frutte de mare are great,
too. I adore it here.
Using morioh’s
wonderful ingredients,
I plan to make you a meal
that will tickle the taste buds
and delight your senses.
Okuyasu: Well, all right, then!
What do you think
I should order?
Actually, i’ll choose
after you show us the menu.
Tonio: Menu? I’m sorry,
- but we don’t use those.
- Josuke: Huh?
Okuyasu: What are
you talking about?
What kind of restaurant
doesn’t use menus?
Tonio: Heh. What I serve depends
on the patron i’m serving.
Okuyasu: Well,
you’re serving me,
and I want the menu.
Tonio: That won’t do.
First, I have to examine
the customer.
Then I decide
what to prepare for them.
Okuyasu:
You’ve gotta be kidding!
You don’t let
your customers choose
what they wanna eat
for themselves?!
Tonio: All right.
Let’s see now.
You had diarrhea yesterday.
( Okuyasu gasps )
Tonio: Your intestinal walls
are inflamed,
and it’s obvious
you’re sleep deprived.
Yes, you only got four hours
last night,
which of course explains
the puffy eyes.
( Okuyasu groans )
Tonio: Now let’s see
your left hand.
Mm-hmm. Your right foot
is infected with a fungus.
You also have two cavities,
and your left shoulder
is stiff, yes?
Okuyasu: What?! How the hell
did you know all that?!
Everything you said
was right on the money!
Tonio: It’s all in the hands,
amico mio.
They are like a window
into your health.
( Josuke sighs )
Tonio: Oh, please excuse me.
And what will you be having,
signore?
Josuke: Oh,
i’m not all that hungry,
but i’ll take a cup of coffee
if you have any.
Make it a cappuccino.
Tonio: Ho capito, signore.
Josuke: This guy
can talk up his fancy dishes
as much as he wants.
Healthy food
tastes like dog shit.
If it’s even
a little disgusting,
we don’t have to pay for it.
We can just complain and leave.
Okuyasu: Roger.
( Gasps )
Josuke: Hmm?
Okuyasu: Hey, josuke,
this water.
No, wait.
It has to be mineral water.
Josuke: What about it?
Okuyasu: I-i’ve never
been as totally sure
about something
as I am right this moment.
This is the best water
that i’ve ever tasted.
( Gasps ) Amazing!
It’s overflowing
with sophistication!
It’s like something
a mountain Princess
playing a harp would drink as
she strums a beautiful melody!
It’s wonderfully fresh
and smooth,
like that glorious
first taste of water
after wandering
in the desert for three days!
Josuke: Wow.
Yeah, you weren’t joking!
It’s amazing!
( Okuyasu squeals )
Divine!
Josuke: You’re right.
It’s first-rate.
I wonder if he’ll tell us
what brand of water it is.
Okuyasu: You know,
this water’s so good,
I think i’m actually
gonna shed a few tears over it.
Josuke: Come on.
A little sip of water
isn’t worth weeping over,
no matter how good it is.
Okuyasu: It must be its purity.
Do you have
a handkerchief on you?
The waterworks
are in full force.
( Sobbing )
Eh? The tears just keep coming!
They won’t stop!
Josuke: Uh, okuyasu,
you’re acting weird, man!
Are you okay?
( Okuyasu wails )
Josuke: What the--okuyasu!
Okuyasu: Holy shit!
What the hell is going on
with these tears?!
They just keep
pouring out of me!
Josuke: Hey, okuyasu! I-I don’t
wanna freak you out even more,
but the white parts
of your eyes,
they’re getting
all shriveled and loose!
Tonio: Momento!
Please try to remain calm.
Josuke: You bastard! The hell
did you give okuyasu to drink?
Tonio: Tranquillo, signore.
His eyes have only
been temporarily withered.
He had
50,000-year-old mineral water
made from melted snow
procured from mount Kilimanjaro
in Africa.
It flushes the eye’s interior
of harmful contaminants
and is an effective treatment
in cases of sleep deprivation.
The reason you didn’t cry
after drinking the water
is because you obtained
an adequate amount
of sleep last night.
Okuyasu: Josuke!
I’m not sleepy anymore!
To be perfectly honest with you,
I feel spectacular,
like I slept a full ten hours!
- ( Laughing )
- Josuke: Wait a second.
You can’t be serious.
Are you telling me there’s
nothing wrong with your eyes?
Okuyasu: Exactly.
When you drink water this good,
it’s only natural
for the tears to flow.
Trust me, josuke. It’s nothing
to be worried about.
I cried way more than this
when I watched "champ" on video.
Thanks for caring,
but I feel like a billion yen.
Josuke: Is that a fact?
Okuyasu:
You bet your ass, it is.
Tonio: Here’s your cappuccino.
Josuke: Oh, thanks.
Tonio: So shall we continue
with the next course?
( Okuyasu sighs ) Wow.
Looks scrumdiddly-yumcious.
Tonio: For our antipasto,
i’ve prepared insalata caprese
with mozzarella.
Okuyasu: ’scuse me,
but what’s mozzaza?
Tonio: Goodness, you’ve never
heard of mozzarella before?
It’s a soft, low-fat cheese
that’s quite tasty.
It is a national favorite
in Italy.
The first people to use tomatoes
as a culinary ingredient
were the Italians.
The Italian people
lead the entire world
when it comes
to tomato-based cuisine.
I’m not bragging.
It’s the honest truth.
We take pride in our work.
Now, I hope you enjoy
your meal, sir.
Okuyasu: Trust me. I will!
Tonio: Hmm.
( Okuyasu murmuring )
( Swallows )
Well, this dish is pretty good.
I’ll give you that.
I dare say this is very good.
But, even so, the cheese itself
doesn’t leave
much of an impression,
which is a shame
after all the hype.
Tonio: No, no. It’s not meant
to be eaten by itself.
You have to add tomato to it.
Okuyasu: Say what?
Adding a tomato sounds weird.
Well, all right,
but here in Japan,
we have sensitive palates.
This is gonna
have to be mind-blowing
to pass the tasty test.
Oh, my god!
- Josuke: Huh?
- ( Tonio chuckles )
Okuyasu: It’s incredible
how the tomatoey nectar
gently caresses
the fresh, delicate cheese!
What a great combination.
The cheese and tomato
enrich each other!
It’s a perfect symphony,
I tell you,
a Harmony
of tantalizing flavors,
a dynamic duo the likes
of Simon and Garfunkel
or even Abbot and costello.
It’s like the writer-illustrator
team asao takamori
and tetsuya chiba
from the comic "ashita no Joe"!
Tonio: Grazie!
Nothing makes me happier
than knowing
you enjoyed my cooking.
Josuke: Hey, ol’ buddy, ol’ pal,
do you think you could share
some of that with your bestie?
Okuyasu: Not on your life.
You can order
your own isasalad canichi.
You’re not gettin’ any of mine,
you got that?
Even if you
were starving to death,
I still wouldn’t give you
a piece of this yummy goodness.
Josuke: Ahh...
Okuyasu: Ahh...
Mmm. ( Chuckling )
So good!
Everything i’ve been through
has been worth it
to get me to this moment!
Josuke: Dick! I knew you
were a stingy son of a bitch,
but this takes it
to a new level!
All right, fine. I will have
the same thing he’s having.
Tonio: Ho capito.
That said...
The only one getting his
stiff shoulder corrected today
will be the gentleman
sitting to your left.
Josuke: Huh?
Okuyasu: Huh? Stiff shoulder?
But, you know,
I am starting to get
a little bit hot
under the collar,
and, for some reason,
i’m all sweaty.
Tonio: Signore...
Might I humbly suggest
you remove your jacket?
Okuyasu: What the hell?
Why am I so itchy
all of a sudden?!
( Wails )
What’s going on?
What’s all this flaky stuff
sticking to my fingers?!
Tonio: Semplice. It’s dead skin.
Okuyasu: Dead skin?!
Tonio: This is proof
that we’ve greatly improved
your metabolic function
and circulation.
The calcium, vitamins,
and minerals of the antipasto
have stimulated your thyroid
and its metabolic
hormone secretion.
Okuyasu: God damn it...
Tonio: The harmful cells
are being expelled
as dead skin, which is
why you’ve been overcome
with an itching sensation.
Tonio: Molto bene, signore.
Keep scratching like that,
because at the rate
you’re going,
the dead skin’ll be gone
in no time.
( Okuyasu whimpering )
( Screams )
Josuke: Okuyasu! Come on, man.
You have to cut it out!
This dead skin’s
the size of a softball!
You’re digging
into your shoulder’s muscle now!
Okuyasu: N-no!
You’re wrong, josuke!
I’m so limber!
My shoulder
is crazy flexible now.
It’s so springy and light,
it’s almost like i’m floating.
( Sighs ) Check it out.
My shoulders have never
been supple enough
to bend around like this.
It’s almost like
I don’t have any bones at all.
( Laughs ) The stiffness I had
is good and gone!
Tonio: Hmm.
( Ball thumps )
If you’ll excuse me,
i’ll be heading
back to the kitchen.
That pasta isn’t going
to get up and serve itself
while we stand here and chat.
( Okuyasu sighs )
He’s amazing!
Actually, he’s incredible.
We should come here
to eat more often!
( Josuke thinking )
I don’t think so.
This is getting way too freaky.
There is something seriously
weird about this guy’s cooking.
With the next dish?
This is the primo piatto.
Today is pasta,
spaghetti alla puttanesca.
Narrator:
Known as "whore’s pasta,"
this dish supposedly
originated with prostitutes,
who favored
its easy preparation.
While cheese
is not usually added
to pasta prepared with garlic,
this dish is
a notable exception.
Okuyasu:
This spaghetti, am I crazy,
or does it
have chili flakes in it?
Tonio: An astute observation.
The special sauce
used in spaghetti puttanesca
is one of the oldest recipes
found in Italian cuisine.
And not to brag,
but my hometown, napoli,
is considered its birthplace,
so of course I give it
the highest possible
recommendation.
Okuyasu: Aw, you should
have said that earlier.
I can’t eat anything spicy.
The only kind
of curry rice I can handle
is that mild Vermont curry
that has apples and honey in it.
Oh, and don’t get me started
on wasabi with Sushi.
Ehh...
Agh! I can’t do it!
It’s too spicy!
It’s like eating fire!
Josuke: There’s
a simple solution, then.
Ready?
Don’t eat it.
- Tonio: Hmm?
- ( Josuke sighs )
( Tonio chuckles )
If it’s not to your liking,
don’t force yourself.
I’d be more than happy to remove
the pasta from your bill.
Now, if you’ll excuse me,
i’ll prepare the main course.
I hope the secondo piatto
will suit you better.
But so you know, signore,
I make my spaghetti
to be enjoyed even by those
who have the lowest tolerance
for spicy foods.
Okuyasu: So I can eat this,
even though it’s spicy?
( Slurps ) Hot.
I know tonio’s a master chef.
Anybody with taste buds
would agree.
And if you ask me,
i’d even say the guy’s a genius,
but this really
wasn’t his best work.
Josuke: No,
I think you lucked out
with your spice intolerance.
Okuyasu: Huh?
Josuke: Hasn’t it
crossed your mind
that this food and water
might be a little too weird?
Something’s shady.
Okuyasu: What do
you mean by shady? Spicy!
Josuke: You scratched off
a softball-sized wad
of dead skin,
and that’s after you cried
a freakin’ river.
Okuyasu: I guess I did,
but that time I went
to shirabu onsen in yamagata,
I lost even more dead skin
than I did today,
and my back got better.
It’s totally normal, isn’t it?
Hot!
Josuke: Listen!
Remember what I said
about that little chat
with hazamada in the hospital?
Hazamada: I don’t know why,
but it seems that stand users...
Josuke: He said stand users
are inadvertently
drawn to each other.
Okuyasu: Josuke! Are you
really trying to tell me
tonio’s a stand user?
Josuke: Shh!
We can’t say for sure yet,
which is why I chose
the word "shady."
Okuyasu: Got it. Shady.
Ah, come on! Why’s it so hot?!
Josuke: If you
can’t handle spicy food,
maybe you should quit trying to
stuff it in your mouth already!
Okuyasu: You’re right.
I should just give up on it.
Spicy food and me
don’t mix at all.
That’s true,
but for some reason,
I can’t stop tasting
this delicious sauce.
( Josuke gasps )
( Okuyasu grunting )
Josuke: Why are you
eating that?!
Okuyasu:
Yeah, it’s weird, right?!
I wouldn’t usually
be able to chow down
on anything this spicy,
but now...
♪
I can’t stop.
After that first bite,
the spice bit back
and won’t let go.
It’s like eating your weight
in beans during a festival,
and even though
they don’t taste good,
before you know it,
you’ve eaten a whole bag,
and you don’t regret
a damn thing,
’cause all you can feel
is your body wanting more!
Josuke: Hey! I told you
to stop eating that crap!
( Okuyasu groans )
I can’t explain it,
but i’m getting even hungrier!
The more spaghetti I eat,
the more of it
I wanna scarf down!
Mmm! Tasty!
Josuke: Okuyasu, calm down!
Okuyasu: Huh?!
( Both gasp )
Josuke: Holy shit! Your tooth!
Okuyasu:
That’s the cavity I had!
The rotten tooth just fell out!
( Groaning )
Actually, I think
one of the bottom teeth
had a cavity, too.
( Yelps )
I was right!
Another rotten tooth!
( Josuke gasps )
( Okuyasu moans )
( Screaming )
Josuke: Whoa! A new molar
is already growing in!
( Okuyasu giggles )
Josuke: I’ve had enough of this.
Time to find out what
that chef from hell’s planning.
Do it, shining diamond!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Okuyasu: Aww.
But I wasn’t done with that.
Josuke: Sorry to ruin the meal,
but i’m reverting
the ingredients
back to their original forms.
♪
- ( Stand growls )
- ( Both gasping )
( Stand growls )
Okuyasu: Hey, what in the world
were those little things,
josuke?
Josuke: It’s a stand.
So my hunch was right after all.
Tonio trendy’s a stand user!
- ( Okuyasu groaning )
- ( Josuke gasps )
Josuke: Okuyasu, are you okay?
Okuyasu: My sleepiness
is finally gone,
my stiffness melted away,
and my cavities
were replaced, but...
My stomach hurts! Agh!
I’ve never felt such
excruciating pain in my life!
- ( Groaning )
- Josuke: Hang on.
Tonio! What the hell
are you trying to pull?!
♪
Where is he?
Eh?
So he’s already finished
our main course.
( Crunching )
- ( Gasps )
- ( Dog crunching )
Tonio: Eccellente.
I want you to enjoy it.
( Chuckles )
Judging from this,
it appears my main dish
of lamb with apple relish
was a success.
( Dog snarling )
- Josuke: What?!
- Tonio: Hmm?
What exactly do you think
you’re doing back here?!
Did you see?!
( Josuke gasps )
( Tonio growls )
Answer the question, per favore!
Did you enter my kitchen
to spy on me?!
Now prepare yourself, signore!
You’re going to pay dearly!
Josuke: Give me one good reason
why I should stand here
and listen to you hurl around
threats about making me pay?!
I should threaten you!
Now, what the hell
are you trying to do
with that food of yours?! Eh?!
( Okuyasu gobbling )
Josuke: Eh? Okuyasu!
Wait a sec.
What are you eating now?!
Okuyasu: I can’t stand it!
My stomach hurts,
but I can’t stop eating!
The tangy-sweet apple relish
combined with juice
from the lamb
makes every single morsel
pure ecstasy!
Who knew food could taste
this finger-licking good?!
Josuke: For the love of god,
drop the meat!
Okuyasu: This is
the best day ever!
It’s like a waterfall
of pleasure washing over me!
Amazing!
( Gags )
( Gasps )
What?! My guts fell out!
( Groaning )
( Tonio chuckles )
Okuyasu: My stomach’s dying!
( Groaning )
- ( Josuke gasps )
- ( Okuyasu gags )
Josuke: Okuyasu!
( Tonio growls )
I’m putting an end to this!
( Josuke gasps ) Oh, no.
Tonio:
Wash your disgusting hands
with soap this instant!
- Josuke: Eh?
- Tonio: Honestly,
entering a kitchen without
permission is inexcusable!
Ascolti.
Cleanliness in the kitchen
is priority one, amico mio!
Josuke: Wait. Wash my hands?
You aren’t trying to kill me?
Okuyasu: Hey, josuke,
it’s like my insides
have been rejuvenated.
Not only that,
i’m completely full
- and feel as fit as a fiddle.
- Josuke: Huh?!
Okuyasu: And best of all,
my diarrhea tummy’s all better!
Josuke: What?!
( Tonio chuckles )
Oh, my,
that’s wonderful to hear!
I love knowing that my cooking
brought happiness and health
to a customer.
Believe me when I tell you
there’s no greater sense of joy
and accomplishment for me
than nurturing a hungry soul.
- ( Dog barking )
- Okuyasu: Huh?
Josuke: Eh? The puppy.
Tonio: With such
unconventional flavors,
I wanted him
to taste-test it.
Our furry friend here
was having a bit
of a digestive problem, too.
Josuke: So you mean
you just wanted okuyasu
to eat a good meal?
You don’t have ulterior motives?
Tonio: Hmm? What else
could a chef want from a patron
but for them to enjoy the food?
The thought gets me out of bed
in the morning.
It’s everything
I could ever hope for.
Josuke: And to be clear,
you’re a stand user.
( Tonio gasps )
Josuke: We have them, too.
( Okuyasu chuckles )
Tonio: Oh!
I can’t believe my eyes!
( Stands gasp )
Tonio: Where to start?
A while back,
I was traveling the world
in search
of the perfect cuisine
when, out of the blue,
I discovered I had
these fantastical powers.
Never in my wildest dreams
would I have thought
i’d meet others
similar to myself.
Even so, that’s no excuse!
You have to possess
common sense!
You touched my kitchen without
washing your filthy hands!
If I was cross with you earlier,
it’s because i’m aware
that a kitchen’s worst enemy
is germs!
Josuke: What? Uh, oh, i’m sorry!
That didn’t even cross my mind.
Tonio: I hope you’re ready
to put in some work.
Now, shall we continue
the cooking?
Okuyasu: Dessert is pudding?
Hah! I’m too manly
for this stuff.
Well, i’ll eat it, but it
doesn’t mean i’m gonna like it.
Oh, my god!
You really are a genius!
You are amazing,
a brilliant artist.
Josuke: Yeah, yeah,
yuck it up, okuyasu.
Tonio: It sounds as though
he’s enjoying dessert.
- ( Dog barks )
- Hmm?
This kitchen isn’t
going to scrub itself!
Josuke: Aw, man,
this is the worst.
Okuyasu:
My athlete’s foot is gone!
Tonio: I shall await
your return, my new friends.
Molte grazie.
( Entry bell rings )
( Sand crunching )
Man: Unless i’m mistaken,
you’re jotaro kujo.
I’m with
the speedwagon foundation.
Until you hear otherwise,
any electrical wiring,
including phone lines,
poses a threat,
and that’s why i’ve come to
deliver this message in person.
"At noon tomorrow,
I expect to arrive
in the port of morioh..."
♪
"Joseph joestar."
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪