Koichi: Ever since last night,
i’ve had this weird feeling
that there’s something important
I have to do,
but I can’t remember what
oh, man.
Why do my shoes and bag
feel heavier than usual today?
Hold on.
♪
Th-this house.
How strange. Somehow I ended up
walking all the way back
to rohan’s house.
The door’s open.
I’d like to drop in
and thank him
for being
such a great host yesterday,
but i’ll be late for school.
I probably shouldn’t.
being an artist,
he’s probably still asleep.
It’d be rude to just barge in.
I really shouldn’t.
( Door creaks )
♪
( Pencil scraping )
( Koichi thinking ) Rohan.
he’s working with
such a chilling expression.
And for some reason,
I can’t shake the feeling
that being in this house
is actually terrifying.
But why?
Rohan: You finally made it.
It’s good to see you.
You’re right on time.
Koichi: Huh?
Rohan: Sorry,
but could I ask you
to wait there
for just a moment?
Two more pages, and next week’s
manuscript will be complete.
it’ll only take
about 20 minutes or so.
Koichi: Did he say he could
finish two pages in 20 minutes?
That can’t be right.
I must have misheard him.
He couldn’t possibly draw
two pages from scratch
in such a short amount of time.
And they’re for next week?
When we were here yesterday,
he’d just finished drawing
the manuscript for this week.
Wha?! He used a pen
right off the bat!
I can’t believe what i’m seeing!
How can he ink
such complex drawings
without sketching first?!
Whoa! He’s not hesitating at all
and is even hammering out
the backgrounds
at the same time!
♪
( Machine gun fires )
His hand movement was so quick!
I didn’t even have a chance
to make out what he did.
( Machine gun fires )
No way! He’s beta coloring
by flicking the ink around
like perfectly aimed shuriken,
and somehow he’s not leaving
a single stray Mark behind!
His technique is incredible!
To beta color without a brush
takes an amount of skill
i’ve never seen before!
You’ve gotta be kidding!
He’s already done?
It only took him
about two minutes
to finish all the beta coloring.
( Rohan chuckles )
and it’s all
thanks to you, koichi.
I’m overflowing
with creative energy.
My body hungers for more.
I have to keep drawing.
Finishing 19 pages
in one night
has been an experience
like no other!
At this very moment,
a masterpiece is forming.
Your life is astonishing.
- Koichi: I don’t get it.
- Rohan: I’m now basing
my entire story on your
life experiences, koichi!
Koichi: What is this?
( Screams )
Rohan: Get cracking!
I want the next reality
from your past.
Hurry, and show me
your next page!
i’m aware
that your weight decreases
with every page I liberate,
but you don’t mind, do you?
It’s a small price to pay
for becoming a masterpiece,
immortalized for all eternity!
( Koichi screams )
I remember!
His power is heaven’s door!
rohan, you’re one
of the enemy stand users!
( Whimpers )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Koichi screams )
Rohan: Well, now, I know
it’s not done just yet,
but this single panel
could be a book all by itself.
fantastic!
I feel like i’m maturing,
both as a manga artist
and a stand user.
And now to read this page.
( Doorbell rings )
- Rohan: Huh?
- ( Koichi gasps )
♪
Rohan: Interesting.
Unless i’m mistaken,
that’s shining diamond’s
josuke higashikata
and the hand’s okuyasu nijimura.
But this doesn’t make any sense.
why would they show up
on my doorstep out of the blue?
There’s just no way
koichi would have mentioned me
to the two of them.
Huh. What’s going on here?
Huh?
( Koichi whimpering )
i don’t know how,
but it’s josuke and okuyasu.
When I didn’t
show up for school,
they must have noticed I was
missing and tracked me down.
( Yelps )
I have to get them to save me!
I’m almost there.
( Grunts )
If I can just open the door,
they can rush in and
get me out of this place!
Josuke: Huh?
koichi: Oh, hey.
This is such a surprise.
What are you two doing here?
And, for that matter,
how’d you even find me?
Both: Huh?
Rohan: I’ll let it be.
Josuke and okuyasu don’t really
interest me at the moment.
For now, i’ll finish up the last
two pages for next week,
and then i’ll procure
even more material from koichi.
( Chuckles )
I can hardly contain myself.
Okuyasu: Huh? You came here
to watch a manga artist
do his work?
How can this guy afford
to work in such a nice place?
rohan kishibe?
Is he famous or something?
Ever heard of him, josuke?
josuke: I’m not
that well-versed in manga.
in fact,
hazamada bitched at me
for not knowing
anything about "perman."
koichi: Wait. What?!
That wasn’t even remotely close
to what I wanted to say to them.
Why am I blanking
all of a sudden?
Josuke: Well, we saw you
staggering around,
so we thought it would be
a good idea to tail you,
but it seems like
everything is a-okay.
I guess we’ll leave you to it.
Koichi: Thanks a lot.
Do you wanna come inside
and observe with me?
josuke: Nah.
Thanks for the offer, though.
Being around famous people
makes me nervous.
Okuyasu: Same. Just knowing
that you weren’t in there
foolin’ around
with some smokin’ hot chick
is enough for me, so i’m out.
Josuke: See you later, koichi.
Koichi: Bye.
( Door creaks )
Why can’t I remember
what I wanted to say?
I’m sure I was
trying to tell them
something really important,
but what was it?
Now I remember
what I wanted to say!
I needed them to rescue me!
Josuke, okuyasu, wait!
See you guys
at school in a bit!
Okuyasu: ’kay!
Josuke: Make sure
you’re not late!
Koichi: I won’t be!
- ( Door creaks )
- ( Sighs )
What was that?! ( Whimpers )
That’s not what I wanted
to say at all!
Damn it! I’m not able
to ask my friends for help.
( Gasps )
we’ve never gone up
against a stand this terrifying.
It’s invincible!
I don’t think we have
nearly enough power
to beat heaven’s door!
Rohan: Ah, I see now.
( Chuckles )
Koichi: At the rate he’s going,
he’s gonna rip out
all my experiences
and leave me a lifeless husk.
Rohan: I sense an infiltrator
has entered the mansion.
What did you do while you
were downstairs? Answer me!
( Koichi gasps )
( Yelling )
( Okuyasu chuckles )
Koichi: Okuyasu!
Okuyasu: Hold it right there!
Just keep looking
straight ahead, buddy.
You’d better not
try anything funny,
or i’ll crush you with my stand,
you doodling dipshit!
koichi: I don’t know how
you figured out I was in danger,
okuyasu, but thank goodness
you’re here!
You are the best!
Rohan: It appears
as though your friend
had a sudden epiphany, koichi.
I didn’t notice it before,
but that small cut on your hand
must have given away
the predicament
you’re currently in.
( Koichi gasps )
rohan: You probably
scratched yourself on something
while you were crawling.
Koichi: I was so focused
on escaping, I didn’t notice.
rohan: That is what
gave it away, right, okuyasu?
And your stand is the hand.
Also, you have
a bit of a complex
regarding your dead brother,
keicho,
and whenever you try
to make a difficult decision,
you wish your brother
was there to do it for you.
Isn’t that right?
( Okuyasu gasps ) Wha...
Who the hell told you all that?
Speak up, punk!
Hey, koichi, tell me everything
about this guy’s stand.
Koichi: Yeah! He’s able to--
I can’t do it.
I can’t say anything that’d
put Rohan at a disadvantage.
If you catch a glimpse of
even one panel, it’s all over.
I desperately wanna
tell you not to look.
Please, don’t look
at that manga.
Okuyasu: Hold it!
Didn’t I tell you
not to move a muscle?!
Rohan: Okuyasu, you were
of no concern to me at first,
but that changed the moment
you entered this house.
Now you’ll serve
as another of my muses.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- ( Okuyasu growls )
Bastard!
What the hell?
Koichi: He’s really fast.
( The hand screaming )
Koichi: Okuyasu!
Okuyasu: What going on?!
Rohan: Josuke higashikata,
I know you’re hiding over there.
( Okuyasu yelling )
Koichi: Okuyasu!
Okuyasu: What the hell is up
with this
freaky-ass manga artist?!
Rohan: Silence.
Now then, koichi,
if you don’t mind,
- I have a question.
- Koichi: Huh?
Rohan: Why do you think
josuke higashikata
is choosing to remain hidden
behind that door?
( Josuke gasps )
rohan: Hmm?
So what do you think?
why won’t he
show himself, koichi?
Koichi: Well, if I had to guess,
i’d say he’s laying low
so he won’t accidentally
catch a sight of your manga.
Rohan: My thoughts exactly.
How very astute of you.
Rohan: Okuyasu knew nothing
about the power
of my heaven’s door,
so he fell for my trap
hook, line, and sinker,
but in doing so, he exposed
the true nature of my stand
to josuke,
causing him to take cover.
I feel that I am somewhat--
no, at this point,
it would appear i’m
at a significant disadvantage.
However, I believe that josuke
has an ulterior motive
for choosing to remain hidden.
What do you think that is?
- ( Okuyasu gasps )
- Rohan: At any rate,
this game of cat and mouse
has gone on long enough.
I suppose i’ll have to resort
to other means
to smoke him out
of his hiding place.
Okuyasu: He’s only hiding,
’cause he wants to figure out
the best way to kick your ass!
( Rohan laughs ) You’re
probably right about that,
but that wasn’t the answer
I was looking for.
No matter, though.
I think i’ve got it.
Our dear hero josuke
is contemplating
whether he should flee
the mansion all by his lonesome.
Some friend, he is.
Koichi: You’re wrong!
Josuke would never
leave us behind!
- Rohan: Right you are, koichi.
- Koichi: Huh?
Rohan: According to your files,
josuke higashikata
has far too much character
to even think
about abandoning you two.
But due to the dynamic nature
of a manga artist’s work,
they tend to consider
every conceivable possibility
at every conceivable moment.
So, in the situation
we now find ourselves in,
what course of action will our
protagonist employ? Let’s see.
Perhaps josuke could flee with
knowledge of my stand’s power,
which would be
quite the dilemma for me.
Okuyasu: You know, running away
might be the best thing
he could do.
He could go and get jotaro,
and if he told yukako
what happened to you,
i’m sure she’d be
angry enough to help us out.
( Koichi yelps )
I’d rather not see her again,
but we could use her hair.
Okuyasu: Josuke,
get out of here,
and tell them what’s going on!
( Groans )
rohan: You imbeciles!
I explained all of that to you
exactly so it wouldn’t happen,
and I doubt you’d be
so quick to prompt josuke
if you knew
what was written in you!
Koichi, i’m giving you
my express permission
to explain the content
of my missive. Let’s hear it.
( Koichi gasping )
Gah! There’s no way!
You can’t be serious!
Okuyasu: Hey, out with it.
What did he write, koichi?
Koichi: How could he do that?
It’s sick.
He’s completely trapped us
in this mansion.
It doesn’t matter what we do!
we’re never
getting out of here!
( Okuyasu growls )
That’s why i’m asking
what the hell this sicko
wrote on my arm, koichi!
Burn myself to death?!
Koichi: That’s why I said
we’re never getting out of here!
You’ll kill yourself if josuke
so much as lifts a finger
to help us!
( Josuke gasps )
( Okuyasu growls )
Hey, wait a second.
he thinks
i’ll burn myself to death?
( Laughs )
That’s total crazy talk.
As if i’d ever do something as
messed up as setting myself on--
hmm?
Koichi: That’s just it!
you will!
We’re completely incapable
of defying him!
Okuyasu: Come on, right hand!
Knock it off! This is so wrong!
( Screams )
( Josuke gasps )
Rohan: So you’ve come out.
Koichi: Like he
really had a choice!
He was basically
dragged out here,
because he couldn’t bear
to hear us suffer!
rohan: Oh.
That’s a rather childish move,
but closing your eyes
could be effective.
There’s nowhere to run
in this cramped room.
If he managed to knock me out,
heaven’s door
would release its grip,
and okuyasu
wouldn’t commit suicide.
( Okuyasu screaming )
Koichi: Josuke, help!
♪
Closing his eyes
is simple-minded,
but it just might work.
As long as he doesn’t see
the manuscript,
heaven’s door is powerless.
Come on. Keep charging.
Rohan: Eh, a pretty good plan,
but all I have to do now is find
a way to force your eyes open.
Think fast!
( Josuke grunts )
rohan: What’s this?
He’s powering through the pain.
If he keeps charging at me
like a stampeding bull,
things are
going to get very ugly.
If I were a manga protagonist,
what would I do
in this situation?
How would I get my enemy
to open his eyes?
Koichi: Keep going, josuke!
okuyasu:
For pete’s sake, hurry up!
Rohan: That’s it.
Surely something in koichi’s
file will be able to help.
There, exactly what I needed.
It seems certain comments
set you off,
such as,
"your hair is laughable,"
or, "wasn’t that pincushion
on your head
in fashion,
like, two decades ago?"
Or maybe, "you think that hair
looks cool, don’t you?"
- How’s that?
- ( Both gasp )
Rohan: I guess
remarks like those
really do set him off.
i must admit
it’s hard to believe,
but the files
are always accurate.
What a preposterous
achilles’ heel.
♪
Josuke: What the hell
did you say?! Huh?!
okuyasu:
Just take it easy, josuke!
Josuke: I dare you
to insult my hair again!
Rohan: If you insist.
Fine. Here goes.
You might think
your hair looks cool,
but in actuality it may be
the shittiest hairstyle
i’ve ever had the misfortune
of laying eyes upon!
( Josuke gasps )
Rohan: Though to be fair,
that nest atop your useless
noggin may come in handy
should a pigeon come by
and decide to roost.
But that’s a very strong "may."
( Both scream )
( Shining diamond yelling )
Rohan: Now witness
heaven’s door!
I win.
( Groaning)
( Koichi gasps )
Okuyasu: How the--
( shining diamond yelling )
Rohan: How is this happening?!
I’m certain his eyes were open,
and he got a full flash
of the manuscript,
so why hasn’t my stand’s ability
taken effect?!
koichi: Huh?
We’re back to normal!
Okuyasu: You’re right.
( Rohan groaning )
I know I showed him
the page, so why--
- ( josuke growls )
- ( Rohan gasps )
Josuke: Where the hell
did you slither off to?!
( Grunts )
Get out here, you punk bitch!
Okuyasu: Hey, I don’t think
he can see straight right now.
koichi: Can’t see?
Hold on. Are you trying to say
rohan’s stupid insults
worked him up so much
that he doesn’t even realize
what he’s doing?!
Josuke: Come on out,
you manga-obsessed asshole!
I got a story for you!
Okuyasu: Yeah. It doesn’t matter
if it’s from a comic
or someone’s mouth.
if he hears
any kind of hair insult,
he flies into a blind rage.
( Josuke yells )
Koichi: Incredible.
i had no idea
his temper was this bad.
I don’t think i’ve seen anything
like this in my entire life.
Rohan: What the hell?
( Koichi gasps )
Rohan: This is a facet
of josuke’s personality
that even koichi
knew nothing about,
so it wasn’t in his file
like everything else.
Though I still don’t get it.
Why does he get so upset
over his hair?
There has to be a reason,
but what is it?
josuke:
Whoever insults my hair
will get the full brunt
of my fury.
I won’t stand for that bullshit!
Koichi: Now that
I think about it,
i’m positive josuke told me
the reason behind his freakouts
when it comes to people
insulting his hair,
but it’s kind of
an involved story.
okuyasu: Huh?
What are you talking about?
Koichi: It all happened
when josuke was a little kid,
and, uh...
( Wind blowing )
I’ll try to remember
the story as best I can,
but I might have to fill in
some gaps along the way.
( Engine grinding )
Josuke was four years old,
and he’d passed out
from an inexplicably high fever.
For 50 days, no one knew
whether he would live or die.
Tomoko: Josuke.
( Engine grinding )
Koichi: He found out later on
that all of this happened
right around the time jotaro
and Mr. Joestar were in Egypt.
They traveled there
in order to defeat
a heinous stand user named dio.
Josuke’s mom had no idea
what was happening,
so she loaded him
in the car and headed
to a hospital in s city
as fast as she could,
but at the time,
morioh was in the middle
of its worst blizzard
in 18 years.
( Tomoko groans ) No use.
What do I do?
( Josuke panting )
Tomoko: Nobody ever uses
this back road anymore,
and there’s not
a damn pay phone in sight.
I’m an idiot. I should have
called for an ambulance!
Why did I bring josuke
out in this snow?
What’s wrong with me?
Koichi: That’s when it happened.
♪
( Tomoko gasps )
Hey, what the hell do you want?!
Just go away, you creeper!
( Josuke panting )
Tomoko: Eh?
( Taps glass )
Tomoko: Got it.
( Gasps ) Thank you so much!
( Josuke panting )
♪
Koichi: Eventually his mom tried
to search for the young man,
but she couldn’t find
any trace of him.
While the stranger
may not have personally
saved his life that night,
as far as four-year-old
josuke was concerned,
that young man he encountered
was a hero unlike anyone
he’d ever seen before.
He became josuke’s role model
and a shining example of what
it means to be a good person.
When someone insults
that part of him,
it triggers something
deep inside his heart.
Josuke: I still don’t know
who he is or where he’s from,
but in honor of him
coming to our rescue,
I decided to adopt
his hairstyle.
No one is allowed
to disrespect it,
no matter who they are.
Disrespecting my hair
means disrespecting him.
Koichi: As far as i’m aware,
that’s the reason
he flies off the handle.
But I have to admit, I thought
josuke was just making it up,
so I wasn’t listening
very carefully.
okuyasu: Huh.
I’ve never heard that story.
( Rohan gasping )
( Koichi yelps ) Careful!
Rohan’s holding a pen!
Okuyasu: You bastard! Don’t know
when to call it quits, do you?!
Rohan: No, that’s not it!
I wanted to make sure
i wrote down
that beautiful story
before I lost consciousness.
( Groans ) What a tale. Bravo.
And I had an amazing experience
to boot.
I’m overjoyed. Experiences like
this happen once in a lifetime.
Such great inspiration.
( Laughs )
How lucky am I?
I’m so glad I packed my bags
and moved to morioh.
Okuyasu: It’s no use.
As long as he’s alive,
he’ll keep searching
for manga material,
even if he ends up
battered and bruised.
Koichi: At this point, you have
to commend his determination.
Putting aside good and bad
for a minute,
he has one of the most admirable
work ethics i’ve ever seen.
Rohan-sensei is truly
a super manga artist!
Josuke: I’ve finally found you,
manga artist!
last I checked,
I wasn’t done punching you!
( Rohan shrieking )
Okuyasu: His determination
is pretty commendable, too.
Koichi: Um, yeah.
( Both yelling, grunting )
Narrator: Due to
an unforeseen illness,
Rohan kishibe’s "pink dark boy"
will be on hiatus for one month.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪