( Boys gasping )
Banker: Congratulations
on this momentous occasion.
You boys came very close
to missing the cutoff date,
but there’s no doubt.
What you’ve brought us
is the third-place
lottery ticket
worth five million yen.
And with that being said,
take this.
It’s the promissory note
you’ll use
to receive the five million yen.
It’s standard procedure.
Please allow us
three days to process
before collecting
your winnings.
( Boys swallow )
Shigechi: Holy wowzers.
Okuyasu: One, ten,
hundred, thousand...
Josuke: What?
It’s got six zeros.
( Banker laughs )
( Grumbles )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
banker: Now then,
if you gentlemen don’t mind,
there’s something
i’d like to ask you.
( Boys gasp )
Banker: It’s regarding
your winning ticket.
Refresh my memory, if you would.
Which store did you say
you procured it from?
( Sniffs )
Josuke: You wanna know
where we got it?
( Both gasp )
Josuke: Why would you wanna know
something like that?
Is there a problem?
Banker: No, it’s a simple
formality. You understand.
( Thinking )
Dimwitted ding-dongs.
You expect me to believe you
won five million yen? Puh-lease!
My teller senses
have never failed me,
and you hoodlums
reek of foul play.
Dear me, what’s this?
Am I sensing hesitation? Odd.
Josuke: Oh, no, your question
just caught me off guard is all.
We bought the ticket in morioh.
Banker: Really? Well I have to
tell you that’s very peculiar.
Not a single store in morioh
sells lottery tickets,
so I find your story
hard to swallow.
( Boys groan )
Banker: Huh.
( Boys stammering )
Josuke: Uh, oh, yeah,
that’s right.
We must have picked it up when
we went to s city the other day.
of course.
It’s all coming back to me.
We bought so much stuff
that day, I totally forgot.
Okuyasu: Yeah, what he said.
It was so long ago, you know?
( Shigechi sighs )
- ( Door creaks )
- ( Boys gasp )
Banker: While we’re
on the subject,
i’ve found another discrepancy.
If you look on the reverse side
of the ticket,
you’ll find spaces
for the ticket holder
to write in their name
and telephone number.
Ichiro morishita.
( Boys gasp )
Banker: And unless
i’m losing my eyesight,
the name written here
doesn’t seem to match
any of yours, does it?
Josuke: There’s a name
written on the back?!
okuyasu:
And a phone number, too!
Shigechi: Oh, jeez!
How did none of us
remember to check
for that stuff?
Banker: Hmm?
Josuke: Just ignore him.
Banker: Me, oh, my,
you’ve found yourselves
in quite
the peculiar predicament.
is this
your lottery ticket or not?
I want an honest answer.
Josuke: Oh, yeah.
I know what happened.
A friend gave me his new number,
and I guess I accidently wrote
it on the back. ( Chuckles )
banker: Friend, eh?
Well, why didn’t you say so?
We’ll give Mr. Morishita a ring
and get this entire mess
cleared up lickety-split.
( Both panting )
Banker: It might interest
you gentlemen to know
all lottery tickets
are traceable
to their point of purchase
via their serial number.
If this ichiro morishita fellow
did indeed purchase
a lottery ticket
and can remember
where he bought it,
we’ll be obliged
to confirm his signature.
it’s a tedious process,
but vital for security purposes.
♪
to whom does
this mysterious ticket belong?
- ( Line ringing )
- Depending on our findings,
we may have to turn it over
to the police.
Boys: What?! The police?!
Ichiro: Morishita speaking.
Who is it?
banker: Hello, sir.
I’m a teller at budogaoka bank.
I have a question
only you can answer.
Did a Mr. Morishita
recently purchase
a great year-end lottery ticket?
ichiro: Yeah,
i’m ichiro morishita.
I bought the little sucker.
( Boys gasp )
Ichiro: No doubt about it.
Banker: Yes. Now i’ve got
you dunderheaded delinquents.
i knew you were
lying through your teeth!
Hell would freeze over
before the gods bestowed
the winning ticket on pathetic,
money-grubbing goons like you!
( Both gasp )
Shining diamond: Dora!
Banker: And you’re sure, sir?
You’re positive
you bought a ticket?
Ichiro: Yeah, i’m sure.
Didn’t you hear me?
I must have bought ten of ’em,
but wouldn’t you know it,
they were all duds,
well, except for this one.
Josuke: Normally i’d
change the whole thing,
but this oughta do it.
Banker: We will need
a signature, Mr. Kinoshita,
but the ticket is all yours.
Ichiro: Kinoshita?
My name’s morishita.
Banker: Ahh?!
What? I don’t understand.
I could have sworn it was
the character for "mori."
Uh, your phone number
is 1771-1281,
correct, Mr. Kinoshita?
ichiro: I told you
my name’s morishita, pinhead!
Why are you even wasting
my time with this bullshit?
Maybe you should try
selling me a winner
instead of bugging me
over the damn phone!
( Banker gasps )
So sorry to trouble you.
- ( Line hangs up )
- This isn’t over yet!
You boys wait right there.
recording:
The number you have reached
is no longer in service.
Please check the number of your
desired party, and dial again.
Okuyasu: We told you that
the ticket was ours, teller-man.
Banker: Please accept
my congratulations
and deepest apologies.
Shigechi: Whoo! Happy day!
I got my money!
It was a lot of hard work,
but now i’m
five million yen richer!
Okuyasu: Hey, what is
that supposed to mean?!
You promised we’d get half of
that lottery money! Shigechi!
Shigechi: Huh? Uh...
Did I say that? I don’t recall.
Okuyasu: Ugh. You’re gonna
try and pull that shit again?!
Eh? What are you doin’, josuke?
Why you holdin’ me back?
Don’t tell me you’re lettin’
this roly-poly shit bag
get away with it!
josuke: Oh, no, he’s not
getting off scot-free this time.
this kid’s gloves
are coming off, shigechi.
( Shigechi sighs )
Okuyasu: Now that’s
what i’m talking about.
I knew you wouldn’t
back down from a fight,
especially when there’s
so much on the line!
Josuke: So you
just up and decided
not to split the money anymore.
Is that it?
Sorry, but that’s not gonna fly
when it comes
to this kind of cash.
Shigechi: Mm...
( Stammers )
Here.
this should get
you two beggars off my back.
It’s not like you did anything
to deserve this money.
Think of this handout
as a pity payment
from your friendly
neighborhood shige--
josuke: Whoa!
- No, okuyasu, don’t!
- Okuyasu: Son of a bitch!
You jerk-off! Give it here!
You promised us
half the winnings,
so half is
what we’re gonna get!
Don’t make me say it again!
You got off easy today,
greedy bastard!
Josuke: You always go straight
to using your fists.
You gotta control yourself.
Okuyasu: Talkin’ wasn’t
gonna work on him,
so I thought some manhandling
would do the trick!
( Shigechi gasping )
Josuke: You’re not hurt
too bad, are you?
I want to apologize for okuyasu.
He never should have hit you,
but this just proves it.
Our partnership
isn’t working out,
so I think we’ll hold on
to the promissory note.
That’ll be the best move
for everyone involved.
We’ll cash it in three days,
as planned.
After that’s done, we’ll split
the money the way we said,
and you’ll get half.
( Shigechi gasps )
Okuyasu: Good riddance.
I am so over that asshole.
There’s no way in hell
you’ll catch me
hangin’ out
with that guy anymore.
Joseph: I hear you, but when
you stop to think about it,
we were the ones trying
to exploit him for pocket money.
We should consider
what that says about us.
- Okuyasu: You moron!
- Joseph: Huh?
Okuyasu: That’s not how I see
this situation at all.
the only reason
he got his filthy mitts
on the five million
was ’cause we helped him.
Without us, he’d be lucky
to even get a few thousand,
but instead he gets to
walk away with 2.5 million yen!
( Both gasp )
2.5 million yen!
- Josuke: Yeah!
- ( Okuyasu laughing )
Both: Money! Money! Money!
Money! Money! Money!
Money! Money! Money! Money!
Harvest: It stays with me.
The ticket stays with me.
( Both gasp )
Harvest: I heard everything,
you sneaky douche-bro.
neither of you
is getting a single yen
of my hard-earned winnings.
We got that five million because
of harvest’s amazing ability.
Josuke: Huh?
Shigechi: You scrubs
and your puny stands
are nothing
compared to my harvest.
Want me to prove it to you?
We can go at it right now.
What do you say? ( Growls )
( Both gasp )
Shigechi: Let’s get it on.
( Okuyasu groans )
- why you...
- Josuke: Freakin’ great!
It took the I.O.U.
For the money!
Okuyasu: You are pissin’ off
the wrong stand users,
pineapple head!
Shigechi: Follow me,
and I won’t hesitate
to kill you,
so back the hell off.
Josuke: Shigechi.
okuyasu:
I’m pretty sure this fool
just said he was gonna kill us.
If you’re so big and bad,
sic your stand on us, already!
But the second you do,
get ready to be ripped apart!
Eh? We got a problem, josuke.
Josuke: What is it?
Okuyasu: Somethin’ weird’s
happening in my pants.
( Wails )
Aah! My legs!
There’s something making my legs
itch like a son of a bitch!
Josuke: An itch? Can’t you
take care of that later?
Okuyasu: I don’t know!
you tell me!
- My whole body itches!
- ( Shigechi chuckles )
( Okuyasu gasps )
What is happening to me?!
Josuke: You have to roll up
your pants, okuyasu! Hurry!
Okuyasu: What?!
( Wailing )
How did these freaky things
get in my pants?!
( Shining diamond yelling )
Josuke: Damn, it’s no use.
Knocking just a few
of ’em off is pointless.
We’re gonna have to come at this
from a different angle.
Okuyasu: Ah, damn it!
( Gasps ) Look!
He’s getting away!
Josuke: All right, he’s really
starting to piss me off.
Okuyasu: Join the club.
the guy’s been
pissing me off all day!
Josuke: We’re coming
for you, money!
Just hold on a second!
Okuyasu: This back-stabber’s
about to learn the hard way
what happens to thievin’ punks
who cross the josuyasu duo!
( Shigechi panting )
( Both panting )
Okuyasu: No one makes a fool
out of okuyasu the great
and gets away with it!
i’ll beat him
’til he’s black and blue!
Josuke: At least now we know
he’s not just a greedy bastard.
He’s a complete idiot, too!
Okuyasu: That butterball
may be slippery,
but there’s no way
he’ll be able to run
long enough
to get away from us!
( Laughs ) I told you.
Look at the little dumb-ass.
( Josuke gasps )
( Shigechi chuckles )
Okuyasu: What?!
It’s like he’s a tank,
and harvest is
moving underneath him
like some kind
of bizarre caterpillar track!
Actually it’s more
like a bucket relay.
Josuke: I wasn’t expecting
that kind of speed.
We gotta close the distance!
- ( Cat hisses )
- ( Shigechi laughing )
( Both ) Huh?!
Okuyasu: He’s not
the brightest bulb,
but he’s actually kinda clever
in a weird way.
It’s like he’s acting
on pure instinct.
Oh, no! He got away!
Josuke: Don’t panic yet!
I got a trick up my sleeve!
If he’s gonna have his stand do
all the heavy lifting,
then we’ll just follow suit.
That money’s not getting away.
Okuyasu: I get it!
♪
( Shigechi panting )
It’s mine now,
five million yen.
( Grunting )
Josuke: Did you really think
you could weasel
away from us, shigechi?
Okuyasu: Why don’t
you make harvest
attack us again, porcu-prick?
I can’t wait to pop
each and every one
of your messed-up
little mini-mes!
- Shigechi: Hmm.
- ( Pipes creak )
( Both stammer )
Shigechi: You’ve seen firsthand
how amazing my harvest is.
It can collect anything,
large or small.
( Both yell )
( Shigechi laughs )
even the screws
that hold pipes together.
And don’t forget the bolts.
( Both scream )
josuke: Good plan,
but I think you’re forgetting
about how badass
my shining diamond’s power is!
( Shining diamond yells )
♪
( Shigechi gasps )
Josuke: What’s up, friend?
( Shigechi whimpers )
Okuyasu: You’ve done a real good
job of gettin’ on my bad side,
but i’m still willing
to forgive you.
first I wanna rearrange
that ugly mug of yours, though.
josuke: Come on.
Hand over that I.O.U., shigechi.
It’s over.
Shigechi: I told you two fools
if you chased me,
then i’d kill you.
Josuke: Eh?
( Shigechi chuckles )
Josuke: Wh-what’s going on?
My hands are...
( Sighs )
( Groans ) I can’t get up.
( Gags ) What’s wrong?
Okuyasu! He’s up to something!
You can’t let your guard down!
- ( Okuyasu groaning )
- Josuke: You, too?!
What’s he doing?!
shigechi: You mean
you haven’t figured it out yet?
The two of you are sloppy drunk,
courtesy of this little number!
( Josuke gasps )
Is that alcohol?!
Shigechi: My harvest
can get its hands
on anything
I order it to snatch,
so I had it grab some booze
when we ran
past the liquor store,
and when you
weren’t paying attention,
i injected the hooch
into your stupid, lying bodies.
Well, to be more specific,
I made it squirt
right into your veins.
Josuke: Wait! You what?! Uhh.
( Both gasp )
- Okuyasu: Aw, get off!
- ( Josuke grunting )
Shigechi: When alcohol
goes directly into the veins,
you don’t need that much until
you’re shitfaced and flailing.
Josuke: I knew alcohol could be
used as a makeshift anesthetic,
but I never thought a kid
would figure that out,
let alone use it
to whammy me like this!
Looks like he’s not
a total idiot after all.
No, it must be
his instinct again.
( Okuyasu groans )
He’s dead meat.
I might be a little tipsy,
but there’s no way
that’s gonna stop
me from ending you!
( Gasps )
- ( Screams ) My frickin’ eye!
- Josuke: No!
okuyasu: What are you
waitin’ for, josuke?! Fix it!
josuke: Shit!
Hang in there! I’m on it!
Shigechi: If i’m remembering
everything correctly,
you two dick-wads
called me a whole bunch
of shitty names earlier,
didn’t you?
I’m gonna show you what happens
when you try to pull the wool
over my eyes
and treat me like a dumb kid.
( Josuke groans ) Damn you.
You’re standing there
all high and mighty
when you breaking your promise
is what started this!
I’ve had about all I can take!
Keep this up, and you’re
not gonna like what comes next.
( Shigechi scoffs )
I think you’ve done
more than enough talkin’
for one life, jerk-suke,
and since your stand’s weak,
your bite can’t even
back up your puny bark.
actually,
both of your stands are shit,
so save the demands until you’re
half as strong as harvest.
’til then, take it in the eye!
Okuyasu: Quick, josuke!
close your eye!
- ( Josuke screams )
- Okuyasu: You okay?
Shigechi: Damn! So close.
there’s no point
in closing your eyes, f.Y.I.
Harvest can grab anything,
no matter the obstacle.
Shut those peepers
as tight as you want.
It’ll just tear off
your eyelids
and gouge out the eye.
Okuyasu: We get the point,
shigechi. Stop it!
Just forgive us already.
it’s not like
we wanted this to happen.
Shigechi: Huh?
Was that an apology?
Josuke: Damn it, kid!
i have had it
with your shitty attitude!
Shigechi: Hear that, okuyasu?
Josuke seems to be
on a completely different page
from you.
Okuyasu: Don’t worry about him!
He’ll come around! ( Pants )
But how about we give you this?
( Shigechi gasps )
Okuyasu: It’s the 10,000 yen
you gave me,
plus everything else
I have on me right now.
Take it as our penance for all
the trouble we’ve caused.
please, shigechi, i’m
begging you not to off josuke!
If he gets taken out,
who’ll fix my eye?
( Josuke gasps ) Okuyasu.
Shigechi: Huh? Oh, yeah.
i almost forgot
I gave you that little handout.
I felt so bad for you beta boys,
i decided
the only right thing to do
was bless you
with over 10,000 yen.
okuyasu: Here!
The money’s all yours.
Just have mercy on us,
o strong one!
- ( Shigechi chuckles )
- ( Josuke gasps )
( Okuyasu grunting )
Josuke: Way to use your brain.
You’re trying to lure him in
like catching a raccoon
with a bit of bait!
Once he closes the distance,
bam, you’ll let him have it.
Well, i’ve got your back, buddy.
Go for it, man.
Work your magic.
Shigechi: That’s a good boy.
I don’t know where this newfound
obedience is coming from,
but i’m glad
you know the pecking order.
( Giggling )
Eh? Something wonky’s going on.
Hey, now, okuyasu,
it feels like you’re trying
to lure me in with cash
so you can
attack me with your stand.
But you wouldn’t do that,
would you, old pal?
Ahh! So you were
trying to trick me!
Did you think i’d honestly fall
for a harebrained scheme
as lame as that one?
you must think
i’m some kind of idiot.
Well, no pity for you.
Okuyasu: It’s not like
we needed it anyway.
Time’s run out for you,
little man.
i guess you were
too busy flapping your gums
like a dumb-ass
to realize that you walked
right into the hand’s
striking range!
I’ll claw away the air
and make it teleport,
forcing the ticket out
of your hands and back to us.
Josuke: This ticket is ours.
Shigechi: It belongs with you?
do you know
who you’re talking to?
( Chuckles ) Idiots.
You wasted your time,
’cause i’m about
to take it back.
Josuke: Incredible. You’re
even dumber than I thought.
Your chance of winning
just expired,
and you never saw it coming.
Shigechi: My money!
what do you think
you’re doing to that ticket?!
It’s worth five million yen,
and you’re ripping it up
like it’s trash!
Why would you do that?!
I don’t get you in the least!
What was the point in going
through all this hoopla
if you were just going
to rip it up when you
- finally got your way?!
- Josuke: Because of you.
I needed a surefire way to stop
you from attacking us again.
Since you can’t
restore the ticket
without my shining diamond,
giving up is your best bet.
the fight’s over.
Accept it, and stand down.
Shigechi: Oh, I get it now.
That’s what you’re doing.
Josuke: And off they go!
your victory’s
blowing away in the wind.
Shigechi: I take it all back!
I don’t get any of this!
Why would you throw away
five million yen?!
Have you lost your mind?!
Harvest, bring back
every last piece! Go!
♪
josuke: Holy shit,
you really don’t get it, do you?
Sending harvest on a fetch quest
was the final nail
in your coffin.
okuyasu:
Your last line of defense
is running through the city
looking for paper scraps,
so who’s gonna protect you
from these drunks, huh?
Shigechi: I think I get it now.
( Okuyasu panting )
( Chuckles ) We did it.
Josuke: Since I caught you
lying down on the job,
why don’t we try and
get in a bit of study time?
The scraps of paper
floating around town
are picked up by your harvest,
but after that,
who has the power
to put them back together? Hmm?
I need an answer.
Who can put the scraps back
together with shining diamond?
Shigechi: Y-you, josuke.
Josuke: "Josuke"?!
sounds to me like
you’re forgetting something!
Shigechi: Yes, Mr. Josuke, sir.
Josuke: Ah, now that’s
what I like to hear.
And i’m sure you know the name
of the person who recovered
that I.O.U. From you.
Well? Say his name, half pint.
Shigechi: It’s okuyasu...
- ( Okuyasu growls )
- Shigechi: The great!
josuke: Good.
That’s our special man.
So what do you say we change
subjects and do a little math?
How do we split five million
between three people?
And remember, everyone has to be
happy when all is said is done.
Shigechi: Well,
i’m fine with half.
josuke: Half, huh?!
Did I or did I not just tell you
there are three of us
to consider?
How are each of us
supposed to get
half of the winnings, shigechi?
Good thing we’re studying,
because your math
needs some work, dude!
( Shigechi stammering )
Both: Anyone home?!
Shigechi: Uh...
i guess i’ll
be okay with a third.
Huh?
Now that I think about it,
without your help, i’d still
be collecting old stamps.
Both: Hmm?
Shigechi: I was acting
like a spoiled brat.
We all found that lottery ticket
by working as a team.
If we hadn’t banded together,
we never would’ve pulled it off.
Wow, it’s starting
to make sense.
my greed kept me
from seeing the big picture.
Let’s split everything
fair and square
so we all get what we want.
( Both chuckle )
- Josuke: There we go!
- ( Okuyasu laughs )
Shigechi: I’ve never seen
so much money before!
Okuyasu: It’s five million yen!
Banker: If you’re
interested in a home
for your newly acquired wealth,
your funds would be very secure
at budogaoka bank.
Josuke: You bet
we’re interested!
Okuyasu: We finally did it!
It’s like i’m dreaming!
Shigechi: I have a question.
Didn’t we agree
to split the winnings
between the three of us?
- josuke: Huh?
- Shigechi: Hear me out.
In the interest of maintaining
a fair and just agreement
between us partners,
wouldn’t it be best to include
our stands in this deal?
I mean, fair is fair, after all.
And since harvest is made up
of about 500 mini-stands,
we should split the pot
500 to one to one.
- That’s not an issue, is it?
- ( Both growl )
Josuke: You’re unbelievable!
okuyasu: I thought
you’d learned your lesson,
but you just don’t know
when to stop haggling, do you?!
Shigechi: I was
only messing around!
A third is fine!
Narrator: For some,
that’s far too much money
for high schoolers to have,
but c’est la vie.
To be continued!
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪