Yoshihiro: Years ago,
I took a trip to Egypt,
where I met
an old hag named enyaba.
She told me to fire this arrow
at whoever it desired,
for the impaled
would become my ally.
After the initial shock,
they would witness
a unique power
rising up from the deep recesses
of their soul.
♪
if memory serves,
she referred to them as stands.
Jotaro kujo...
If he and his Minion army
of hit men
are pursuing my dear yoshikage,
then i’ll have to create
my own army,
one like no other,
an army of stand users.
Here we are, arrow.
The time’s come
to select your prey.
Which of these vessels
do you desire?
Huh?
A telephone pole?
Why would you want
a telephone-- ( Gasps )
wait a minute.
You desire that child?
So you’re telling me a child
is to become the first
of my new allies?
( Boy gags, coughs )
Yoshihiro: If that is your will,
i’ll Pierce the lad’s soul
and add him to our ranks!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Camera clicking )
Joseph: Hmm?
- ( Baby giggles )
- Rohan: Hmm.
Joseph: Well, if it isn’t
our manga artist extraordinaire.
Rohan: I hope you’re
having a good morning, sir.
joseph: Hmm.
Snapping a few photos, eh?
Rohan: I’m trying to take
candid shots of office workers
while on their morning commute.
- Joseph: Oh?
- Rohan: Just think about it.
Yoshikage Kira, he stole
someone’s identity, correct?
Well, he’s probably
commuting to work
just as his victim once did.
Joseph: You think?
Rohan: He’s between 25 and 35
and nearly two meters tall.
Add in that he’s
an office worker,
and our suspect pool
dramatically decreases.
Joseph: I see,
but how can you be sure
he uses this exact station?
He could just as easily
commute by car.
Rohan: That could be the case,
but though he may
have changed his face,
it’s very likely that he
will still fall into old habits.
Habits, that’ll arouse
the suspicion
of his cover family.
By now, they must realize
something’s amiss.
Joseph: Hmm.
Rohan: My biggest fear
is that the family
will recognize their intruder,
prompting him
to eliminate them as well.
And don’t you think for a moment
that i’m going soft.
I just want to find Kira
before he wreaks more havoc.
Joseph: Hmm.
Boy: Hey, tall bros!
- Joseph: Mm?
- Rohan: Eh?
Boy: Does one of you wanna
play me in a game of roshambo?
- Ro-sham...
- ( Rohan sighs )
Boy: What? Are you two
deaf or somethin’?
Play with me!
Rohan: What an oddball.
- Boy: Just play already!
- Rohan: I suppose every station
has a nut-job or two
running around.
well, Mr. Joestar,
if you come across any leads,
you know how to reach me.
Joseph: Don’t go sticking
your nose in trouble
all by your lonesome now.
boy: Hey, mister!
Aren’t you that manga artist?
( Laughs )
You stopped drawing
for a little while, right?
I’m a big "shonen jump" fan,
so I know your work.
Now how ’bout it?
it won’t kill you
to play with me, will it?
Rohan: What is
your problem, kid?
Hit the bricks!
Boy: But I just
wanna play roshambo!
It’ll be fun!
( Rohan gasps )
What the? How peculiar.
The boy’s left cheek
has a big hole in it.
It’s so deep, I bet it
extends into his mouth.
Boy: Come on, already! Play me!
No hard feelings
if you win, but...
A draw, and we go again!
If you’re late, then you lose!
Understand?!
Ready? And ro-sham...
Rohan: This kid is
being weirdly tenacious.
( Gasps ) Is he a stand user?
All right, then, ro-sham...
Rohan: Heaven’s door,
shut this brat up!
( Boy gasps )
( Yelps )
( Rohan scoffs )
Hmm. Now let’s see.
It says his name is Ken oyanagi,
age 11.
I’m not seeing anything
about him having a stand.
He got the injury when he fell
from a telephone pole.
Hmm.
Interesting.
He feels compelled to play
roshambo. Bizarre, but...
Driver: Are you two gentlemen
gonna need a ride, or what?
Rohan: Could we trouble you
for 30 more seconds?
( Ken gasps )
- fire away!
- Rohan: Once we do this,
you have to leave me be.
Ken: Ro-sham...
Bo!
( Gasps )
Rohan: Well, so long.
Ken: How could I lose?
Rohan: I suppose i’ve done
enough work for one day.
Okuyasu: Yo, Rohan-sensei!
josuke: Are you
calling it quits for the day?
Instead of sitting
all by yourself,
why don’t you join us?
( Rohan sighs ) Perfect.
A self-absorbed jerk-off,
a moron, and a bitch,
three people I have absolutely
nothing in common with.
hey, guys. Sorry.
I’m working at the moment.
Maybe another time.
- Josuke: Oh. Gotcha.
- Okuyasu: Huh?
Rohan: Hey! You brat!
What do you think you’re doing?
I was going to sit there!
Ken: I bet, but you
never actually sat down.
The seat was free, so I took it.
You snooze, you lose.
You know what I mean?
( Gasps ) Oop.
Rohan: I have had enough!
What is your deal?!
Ken: Let’s settle this
with roshambo.
Winner takes the seat, ’kay?
Rohan: Again?!
( Ken gasping )
( Wailing )
It’s not fair!
I sat here first,
so you can’t have it!
This is my seat, you meanie!
Waiter: Is there a problem here?
Rohan: Uh, we’re fine.
Okuyasu: Rohan-sensei,
why can’t you give him a break?
Come on. Look at him.
He’s just a kid.
Josuke: Yeah, i’m with him.
You’re supposed to be
the mature one.
Yukako: You could try
sitting next to him.
rohan: Shut up!
None of you are helping!
eh, fine, kid!
I’ll play with you again!
Well, that’s what
you’re after, isn’t it?
( Ken chuckles ) Yeah!
That’s more like it!
’kay, now get ready.
Ro-sham...
Bo!
- ( Gasps )
- Rohan: Oh!
Well, would you look at that!
I’m the winner!
Got nothing to say?
i, for one,
have never been so happy
to win a game of roshambo
in my life! Hah!
Boys: You call this
being mature?
( Yukako scoffs )
Rohan: There’s no better feeling
than destroying a smug whelp
at his own game.
( Laughing )
Ken: Damn! Lost again.
( Groans )
♪
Rohan: Oh.
This is some good material.
Who knew such an obscure book
could be found in morioh?
Hmm. 7,500 yen.
Do I have that much?
Eh?
Ken: ’scuse me!
I wanna buy this book!
Rohan: You obnoxious little...
( Stammers )
Ken: Let’s Duke it out,
roshambo style.
Rohan: Fine.
Ken: Brace yourself!
Ro-sham...
Rohan: Rock!
you’re messing
with the wrong artist, punk!
( Ken laughs )
Look at that. I won.
Still think i’m just a punk?
( Laughs )
One win, two losses.
Rohan: What the hell
is going on here?
( Gasps )
( Gasps ) What is this?
What the--
it’s that damn cheek hole.
So I wasn’t off base before!
He might be a user!
What?!
Ken: This is frickin’ awesome!
I never would have guessed
he was hiding something so cool!
I’ve never felt anything
like the energy
flowing into me right now!
It’s totally awesome!
It’s like being supercharged!
Rohan: That’s enough!
Now quickly, heaven’s door,
turn this little brat
into a book!
( Groans )
( Pole clangs )
Judging from his sloppy work,
that must’ve been the first time
he’s used his stand.
However, that doesn’t mean
he won’t master it given time.
Eh? Heh.
"I want to beat the crap
out of Rohan in roshambo," huh?
"Roshambo isn’t
a game of chance.
"It’s a psychological
game of will.
"If I beat Rohan at roshambo,
it means i’ve outwilled him.
"Rohan’s only 20 years old,
"but he lives life
on his own terms.
"His work also inspires
a whole lot of people.
"If I can beat the crap
out of Rohan in roshambo,
"that’ll prove I can be
better than him one day.
"I can’t wait to grow up,
’cause then i’ll be
just as respected
as the great Rohan." ( Gasps )
I knew it!
This kid is well on the road
to becoming a stand user.
The arrow must have
just pierced his soul.
"Ability-- winning in roshambo
"makes my opponent’s energy
my own,
"but I must play five games.
winning two games
only gives me partial energy."
So he needs to win five.
Huh?
It can’t be. How did you...
Ken: So this power’s
called a stand.
That’s pretty awesome.
thought you dodged
a bullet there, didn’t you?
Well, think again,
’cause i’ve already
got a third
of your so-called stand.
( Rohan gasps )
What?! My right arm is gone!
Ken: It sure is,
and 1/3 of its incredible power
is under my control!
That means you can’t poke around
in my head anymore.
Rohan: Damn you!
Ken: Oh, and if I win
two more times,
all of your powers will be mine!
Rohan: You punk! Damn it.
You won’t get away with this!
Ken: Taking a swing at me
like that was pretty ballsy.
Guess you got a taste
of your own medicine.
Rohan: Okay. Now I get it.
i have to defeat you
in another game of roshambo.
That’s the only way i’ll
win back my stand’s right arm.
Game on!
Ken: Here we go!
Completely oblivious
to the plight you’re in?
If you lose just one more time,
you’re finished.
Surely, by now, you’ve realized
you’re all out of chances.
since I know
you’re a stand user,
i’ll show you no mercy.
the moment
I retrieve my right arm,
i’m putting you
out of commission.
Admit defeat.
Ken: Wait. Are you
trying to psyche me out?
Rohan: All right,
let’s get this started.
Ken: I’m not ready
to play just yet.
I won the last match
using paper,
so I guess it’s only natural
to wanna go with rock
or scissors this time,
but it’d be kinda stupid to go
with the obvious, just ’cause--
and it’s pretty clear
to anyone with eyes
you’re not the naïve type,
Rohan-sensei,
so maybe going with paper
would be the best way to go.
I mean, what could
it hurt, right?
Okay, i’ve made up my mind!
Let’s go!
Ro-sham...bo!
- Rohan: What?!
- Ken: I did it!
I outwilled Rohan-sensei
with the power of paper!
( Rohan groans )
ken: That makes
two wins and two losses.
Sucks for you. ( Chuckles )
( Rohan gasps )
♪
( Rohan panting )
( Ken laughs )
I just took the lower half
of your heaven’s door.
If you’re tired, you could
rest on that bench over there.
rohan: No,
that won’t be necessary.
When vanquishing your opponent,
you must savor it
and look down on the conquered
with pity and disdain.
( Ken chuckles )
I’ve got two wins
and two losses,
so we’re both
one game away from destiny,
but i’m so close to victory,
I can almost taste it!
I know I lost twice, but I came
back and won twice in a row.
It’s the other way around
for you. You’ve lost twice.
You’re smack-dab in the middle
of a major losing streak!
( Rohan growls )
( Yoshihiro laughs )
Marvelous!
As expected from one
chosen by the arrow.
We’re almost there.
If this kid can finish
absorbing Rohan kishibe’s
mind-reading powers,
we’ll be unstoppable!
you’ll serve
my precious yoshikage well.
Rohan: Good work. You’ve gotten
better at the mind games.
Quite impressive for a punk kid.
Ken: You’ve lost the game
twice in a row. That’s a fact.
Rohan: Yes, you’re right.
i won’t argue.
Since you’re big on facts,
I take it you won’t mind
if I tell you another?
I’m positive you won’t be
using paper for this duel.
( Ken gasps )
( Chuckles )
Guess we’ll find out, huh?
Rohan: Let’s not get ahead of
ourselves. I’m not finished yet.
I went with rock twice,
and it cost me both times.
It’s obvious now that rock
is my unlucky play. Am I wrong?
- ( Ken grunts )
- Rohan: It goes without saying
i’d be adverse to using rock
again when it’s been so unkind,
and since I won’t be going
with rock this time,
you won’t be able to use paper.
Using it would be the same
as admitting
i’m not on a losing streak,
despite what you said
a while back.
ken: Hah!
You’re still gonna lose!
All right! Let’s do this!
It’s time!
- ro...
- Rohan: Sham...
Both: Bo!
( Ken screams )
Rohan: All that bluffing,
and he still used paper.
What mental fortitude!
Ken: There’s no way
i’m gonna lose to him.
I still have the upper hand
in this match!
I’ll use paper
four times in a row!
This game’s in the bag!
Rohan: Time to go back to rock.
I’ll make misfortune
work in my favor.
Ken: Here we go!
( Rohan groans )
Wh-what’s wrong with my knees?
Ken: Huh? He’s never
moved like that before.
the only move Rohan
hasn’t used yet is scissors.
Crap! Going with paper
four times in a row is risky!
What?! No way!
Rohan: It seems rock
wasn’t unlucky after all.
( Ken gasps )
Yoshihiro: Enh. That bastard!
Huh?
No! That’s not good.
Ken: Eh?
( Chuckles )
Hey, mister!
Can I talk to you?!
So, Rohan-sensei, those two
are probably users, too, right?
- ( Rohan gasps )
- Ken: Yeah, i’m right.
I can feel it in my bones.
Let’s test my luck.
If it all runs out,
those two will head over here
and rescue you,
but if luck is on my side,
coming over here will be
the last thing on their minds.
Josuke: Oh, look at that.
it’s Rohan again.
Ken: Yo!
Josuke: I really
can’t stand that guy.
- Ken: Hello!
- ( Baby fussing )
josuke: Let’s just
smile at him and keep walkin’.
joseph: Well,
I suppose we could do that.
Hmm. Huh?
That child is--
yes, he has to be...
One of rohan’s adoring fans.
See you again soon.
Josuke: Yeah, later, man.
( Rohan gasps )
( Ken chuckles )
Well, what do you know?
Seems luck is still
on my side, Rohan-sensei.
- So are you scared yet?
- ( Rohan gasps )
ken: I’ve never felt
more confident about winning.
As long as i’ve got luck,
i can’t lose!
I feel like I could play
a high-stakes game
of Russian roulette
with five out of six bullets
in the chamber
and still live
to tell the epic tale!
Even a shower of glass
is nothing to me!
♪
( Rohan groans )
( Gasps )
( Ken chuckles )
Now then, it’s time
for the final match.
Who’s gonna win, Rohan-sensei?
( Rohan groans )
Ken: Huh?
What the heck are you doing?
Hurry, and assume
your roshambo pose.
It’s time to play.
Rohan: You’re the one who needs
to hurry up and get started.
I made my move.
You just missed it.
Ken: You can knock off
the jokes, okay.
Rohan: It’s not a joke, whelp.
You said your aim
is to surpass me,
but since i’m a bit older,
i’ll let you in
on a little secret.
Beating one’s opponent
isn’t all that difficult
when you think about it.
What’s really challenging is--
and pay attention.
The real challenge...
Is truly outdoing oneself,
which is what i’m going to do
using my own luck!
( Ken growls )
♪
Let’s go, Rohan!
Time to play!
Ro-sham... Bo!
there we go!
How do you like that?!
( Joints popping )
W-wait. What’s going on?
What?!
Yoshihiro: Huh?!
Ken: Wh-what happened?
Why am I all of a sudden
making the rock move?
( Screams )
Rohan: That makes three wins
and two losses.
Now you’ve got
the unlucky rock.
I couldn’t see it before, but it
wasn’t just Joseph joestar
who paid me a visit.
Luck did, too.
The invisible baby.
( Baby coos )
- ( Yoshihiro and Ken gasp )
- ( Baby coos )
Rohan: You put too much energy
into being given luck,
while I took it upon myself
to make my own.
That is the very meaning
of outdoing oneself.
( Baby coos )
( Ken gasping )
Rohan: Now, then, as I recall,
I promised to put you
out of commission.
I’m going to write,
"as long as I live,
"I shall lose at roshambo,
and my stand
shall be no more. Fin."
( Ken growling )
Just shut up!
Stay away from me, Rohan!
( Rohan gasps )
I swear, if you touch me,
the baby gets it!
- Yoshihiro: Ha hah!
- Rohan: You fool!
Do you have any idea
what it is you’re doing?
( Ken growls ) We’ve moved on
now to a war of words!
You didn’t really beat me
in that match!
you’re nothing but
a lowdown cheat and a coward!
Rohan: Give me the baby.
do it now.
Ken: Battle me one more time!
Do that, and the baby
stays safe and sound.
Rohan: Are you deaf?
Surrender the baby.
I’ll humor you.
( Ken yelling )
Get ready to lose!
Ro-sham...
Bo! Bo! Bo!
( Screams )
Why can’t I win?!
Yoshihiro: Oh! Blast it!
I went through all that trouble
to give you stand powers,
and you blew it!
Sayonara!
Rohan: You won’t die.
I’m simply going to wipe
your stand out of existence.
Ken: No!
I refuse to live life
under the shadow
of your stupid writing.
It’d be worse than death.
I won’t let you play around
in my head! Got it?
i’d rather jump
in front of this giant truck!
Live with that, Rohan!
Rohan: Hmph.
bravo, kid!
I was wrong about you.
People who have a flair
for the dramatic,
comic book-like action,
really know how to pull
at the old heartstrings.
Ken: Huh? Eh?!
♪
What?! But you’re
gonna get run over, too!
Rohan: Think so?
Yoshihiro: Where the hell
did this damn wind come from?!
Driver: Eh? Have mercy!
What’s this picture?!
I can’t see!
My view is blocked!
( Ken panting )
What? It went around us.
You could have been killed,
too, if it hadn’t swerved,
but you--
was it luck?
Rohan: Perhaps, but I must say
you’ve become
quite an interesting person.
I won’t finish you off.
However, you must never use
your stand for evil.
Yoshihiro: It’s just my luck
that I would hit
that truck! Damn!
( Ken sighs ) He beat me.
I’ve completely lost to him.
Joseph: Rohan, wait up!
- Ken: Huh?
- Rohan: Hmm?
Joseph: Hey, you haven’t seen
the baby anywhere, have you?
Josuke: Yeah, the kid has
suddenly gone missing!
( Rohan gasps )
Joseph: What if she’s turned
fully invisible again?
Rohan: Damn it, that’s right.
- Ken: Huh?
- Rohan: She’s gone.
Josuke: Hey, where are you?
Rohan: I’ll just pretend
like nothing happened.
Uh, hey, where’d you go? Baby?
Narrator: Rosham boy,
real name, Ken oyanagi,
stand name, boys man man,
not out of commission,
though the hole
in his cheek remains.
( Baby coos )
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪