♪
Josuke: Nothing.
Both pockets are empty,
other than this piece of paper.
( Yuya gasps )
( Josuke sighs )
Yuya: The scent’s
out of the pocket now.
Could it be?
Josuke: Huh?
this is
just a blank sheet of paper.
( Gasps ) Hmm?
( Gasps )
What?!
( Yuya gasps ) Josuke!
♪
Kinoto: Whoa! ( Gasping )
( Rohan laughs )
Talk about falling
for the obvious!
You know, you should
really be more careful.
i warned you
about the fire damage.
Maybe try listening next time.
♪
i don’t understand why
you were getting so worked up.
It’s a normal back.
( Kinoto stammering )
It’s over for me.
This is the end. I’m finished.
I can’t explain it, but I
have this horrible feeling
that i’ll die
if someone sees my back!
Rohan: Wha--
kinoto: It’s too late now!
I’m as good as dead!
Rohan: I’m sorry.
Just calm down.
It’s my fault.
My curiosity got the best of me.
( Kinoto moaning )
Rohan: What?!
( Kinoto groans )
Rohan: He was
attacked by a stand!
Damn thing must have
been attached to his back!
Which explains why heaven’s door
couldn’t reveal it
when he arrived at the house.
It was already too late
by that point.
That stand attached itself
to him before he got here.
The architect isn’t a user.
He’s a victim.
He was used like a meat puppet
to get to me!
♪
Stand: Piggyback, please.
Rohan: It’s here.
It’s the enemy stand.
( Gasps )
stand:
Let’s play piggyback, okay?
Piggyback, please.
- ( Rohan gasps )
- Stand: How ’bout it?
Can we play piggyback, please?
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
agent: Here’s a list of
missing persons cases in morioh,
including runaways.
The data is from the period
after kira’s disappearance,
hence the small number.
Joseph: You’re of the mind
that some of those people
could be kira’s victims?
Makes a lot of sense.
Jotaro: It’s a possibility,
but we can’t know that for sure.
At this point, we have to follow
his every conceivable move.
It doesn’t matter
how insignificant
the activity seems.
any action he takes
can have far-reaching effects.
They always do.
♪
Stand: Piggyback, please.
Piggyback, please.
Rohan: Heaven’s door, attack!
( Heaven’s door gasps )
Stand: Piggyback, please.
Hey, piggyback, please.
Rohan: What the--
I don’t believe it.
the damn thing has
attached itself to my back!
Is this because
of the architect,
because I looked at his back?!
Blast it!
( Gasps )
Stand: Ignite the pictures.
Please ignite the pictures
you’ve collected.
Rohan: Ignite the what?
Stand: You heard what I said.
now get rid
of those pesky pictures.
Rohan: What do you mean?
( Gasps ) The pictures I took.
could one of them
lead us to yoshikage Kira?
That’s it, isn’t it?
You’re attempting a coverup!
stand: Just set all
the pictures on fire, please.
You’ll do it, won’t you? Please?
Rohan: Shut up, you leech!
( Stand gags )
Rohan: Heaven’s door!
I’ve got it!
How about I read your powers,
then inscribe my mandate?!
What the hell?!
( Groans ) Shit!
Stand: I am known as cheap trap,
and I was given life
when masazo kinoto
was impaled by the arrow,
but, since he croaked,
my user is Rohan kishibe.
I’ve relocated to you!
you’re my user now,
whether you wanna be or not!
- ( Rohan gasps )
- Cheap trap: Get it now?
When you attack me with a stand,
all you’re doing
is hurting yourself.
Scary, right?
i am a stand
with a will of my own.
Sure, masazo kinoto birthed me,
but he didn’t have
the wherewithal to control me
as a stand user.
I filled his mind with lots
of horrifying whispers,
and the terror
of his bony back being seen
consumed him at the very end,
wouldn’t you say?
You understand, yes?
Tell me you do!
You get it, yes?
i whisper fear
into the ears of my host.
Now that you know my power,
burn those pictures!
Rohan: Dirty leech, get off me!
( Grunts )
Damn you, bastard!
I swear i’ll get you
off my back!
cheap trap:
If that’s what you want,
all you have to do
is show me off.
Just show someone your back.
yes, i’ll leave you
and attach to another soul.
It just takes a flash.
- Rohan: Huh?
- ( Bicycle bell rings )
Milkman: Afternoon,
Rohan-sensei!
I’m an avid reader of your work,
though you might
wanna try some nudes.
Nude women, that is!
( Rohan gasps )
- Milkman: Catch you later!
- ( Rings bell )
cheap trap:
Let’s burn those photos, yes?
( Rohan growls )
( Gunshot )
Yuya: Josuke!
He--he caught the bullet.
Josuke: Damn you, asshole!
( Terunosuke chuckles )
Shining diamond, eh?
well, I guess
the rumors were true.
You can indeed handle a bullet
at point-blank range
without an issue.
( Josuke gasps )
terunosuke:
This is freaky, isn’t it?
Now chomp down
on that lip, josuke.
( Josuke shudders )
terunosuke:
He’s almost there. Bite it!
show me that bite!
Show me your Mark of fear!
Josuke: That sheet of paper
must be his stand!
it has to be,
since it’s as pathetic
as that geezer in the photo!
( Terunosuke sighs )
Still won’t bite, eh?
Seems he’s trying to cover up
his fear with anger.
If that’s the case, I suppose
it’s time for the big reveal.
Josuke: You cocky bastard.
You’re dead!
Yuya: Something about this
doesn’t feel right.
He’s been hiding
this whole time.
Why would he choose
to show himself now?
This is all a trap.
He made himself appear
so you’d attack him.
This guy’s dangerous.
get the hell
out of there, josuke!
( Terunosuke chuckles )
You know, you were right
a moment ago when you said
I had a pathetic stand.
But it’s not all bad, I guess.
Its ability allows me
to transform almost anything
into a piece of paper
to be filed discretely
and conveniently.
( Laughs )
- ( Clatter )
- ( Both gasp )
terunosuke:
And this slip of paper
contains koichi hirose.
Josuke: Bastard! So you’ve
had koichi this entire time!
Yuya: I’m picking up
koichi’s scent again.
He wasn’t holding on
to one of his belongings.
He had koichi!
terunosuke:
Rest assured, he’s alive.
I’m the user of a pathetic,
third-rate stand, right?
it doesn’t have
the power or ability to kill.
However, if someone were
to tear it into little pieces,
that’s a different story.
Josuke: I’m gonna
let you off easy.
Bring koichi back now,
and i’ll only beat you down
to a bloody pulp.
terunosuke:
Go ahead, and take him.
I’d like to see you try.
( Josuke growls )
Shining diamond: Dora!
Josuke: Koichi! ( Gasps )
Terunosuke: As you said earlier,
my stand
isn’t the most powerful,
and it doesn’t have
the ability to kill,
but if it were to be
ripped to shreds...
Yuya: I wouldn’t go after
that paper if I were you.
It has to be a trap!
Josuke, ignore it.
♪
terunosuke:
Ah, at long last, you bit it!
( Josuke gasps )
terunosuke:
Misterioso was waiting
for this moment,
josuke higashikata!
The moment you bit your lip,
you sealed your fate.
( Josuke roars )
( Shining diamond yells )
( Gasps )
( Misterioso yells )
Josuke: You devious dickhead!
Terunosuke: You just revealed
your Mark of fear.
( Josuke gasps )
Terunosuke: You can attempt
to resist all you like.
You are now powerless
before misterioso.
( Josuke yells )
( Metal creaks )
Yuya: Sorry, josuke, but i’m
glad we made that agreement.
If I had tried to help,
he would have gotten me first.
i am the one with
the scent-discerning abilities.
♪
Terunosuke: Now that you’ve
fallen prey to its power,
do you understand why misterioso
is the most unstoppable force
ever seen?
( Gasps )
( Josuke grunts )
Terunosuke: What?
How the hell did you get out?
yuya: His stand
is repairing the metal pole,
and he’s using the energy
to escape.
( Josuke pants )
The piece of paper
you’re holding,
if I looked inside, i’m guessing
I wouldn’t find koichi.
I knew from the start
that was just a dirty decoy
with "koichi hirose"
written on it.
The only reason
you had the confidence
to reveal your true self to me
was because you still had
the real koichi held hostage.
Keeping him alive
is the only way
for you to maintain
your leverage.
I knew that piece of paper
was just a trap
to lure me into danger.
- Looks like I was right.
- ( Terunosuke gasps )
Josuke: But, even so,
I still had no other choice
but to go after
that stupid scrap of paper.
Despite it being a trap,
there was still a chance
you’d thrown the real koichi
toward that car,
and when it comes to my friends,
i don’t care
if it’s a 1% chance!
Losing them is a risk that i’m
just not willing to take!
( Yuya gasps )
Josuke: Misterioso
can have the win for now.
it sucks,
but there’s not much more
shining diamond
can do at this point.
That said, let me give you
a piece of advice
before I become
one of your paper prisoners.
rip me to oblivion
the moment I finish folding,
’cause if i’m able
to make it out
of this bullshit trap alive,
i’ll freakin’ kill you!
♪
( Terunosuke laughs )
That’s a pretty loud bark
you had there.
hmph. It’s too bad you
didn’t have the bite to match.
Hmm?
( Growls )
( Yuya gasps )
Terunosuke: Yuya fungami,
allow me to commend you.
Not assisting josuke
was a very wise move.
I could have easily disposed
of you, had you tried.
Your Mark of fear
is a stroke of the chin!
in fact,
you’re doing it right now!
But the old man in the photo
never ordered me to kill you,
so I suppose your death has been
postponed for the time being.
Smart move, my friend.
♪
want to hear
something interesting?
This paper, it’s tough,
but anyone can release
its contents by unfolding it.
Straightforward, yes, but for
someone consumed with fear,
it’s surprisingly difficult.
( Yuya gasps )
terunosuke:
Morioh grand hotel, please.
Yoshihiro: Excellent!
koichi hirose
and josuke higashikata
have been disposed of!
Rohan kishibe should be enjoying
the same fate about now.
( Laughs )
Rohan: Which one?
which one
exposes yoshikage Kira?
Which picture is that old man
so worried about?
cheap trap:
Just burn them all, okay?
rohan: No use.
There just aren’t enough clues
for me to figure this out.
Cheap trap: Well, then,
let’s burn them, yes?
Rohan: Shut your mouth,
you pest!
damn it.
I have to let them know.
Someone needs to know
what’s going on!
Driver: Uh, that was
morioh grand hotel, right?
terunosuke:
Yes, that is correct.
Driver: Are you
spending the night?
terunosuke:
Not sure, though I do have
a lot of work to take care of,
a lot of work, indeed.
Highway go go: No, I cannot
allow you to reach that hotel.
- ( Terunosuke gasps )
- ( Feet thumping )
yuya: Damn it, josuke,
you’re such a pompous asshole.
♪
Seeing you get captured makes me
think about my darling girls.
I can’t believe i’m saying this,
but if any one
of my loving, supportive vixens
was ever turned into
a piece of paper, i’d--
i don’t even
wanna think about it,
but if they were nabbed
by this creep,
i’d do the same thing
to get them back!
highway go go:
If I let you or Kira get away,
i’d never be able to look
at myself in the mirror again.
I order you to release koichi!
Terunosuke: I rescind
my earlier statement.
This is a most unwise decision.
Listen, i’m not sure you really
want to take me on, coward.
Doing so would instantly make
you an enemy of kira’s father.
But so be it!
Yuya: 63, 64, and 65.
It’s not a tank,
but highway go go
is a relentless hunter.
if you think you’re
getting away, you’re wrong!
( Tires squeal )
( Gasps )
It stopped, but why?
We’re not at the hotel yet.
And it doesn’t look like
anybody’s in the taxi.
Huh. Strange.
I’m still picking up his scent
from the car.
But how? Where the hell is he?
Where could he have run off to?
( Highway go go gasps )
The scent of this paper...
There’s no question.
This paper smells
like koichi and josuke.
Yuya: Wait, highway go go!
Don’t open the door just yet.
The bastard thinks i’m an idiot.
This is clearly another trap.
So he’s attempting
to lure me in, huh?
Fine! I accept your challenge!
Did you hear me?!
I said i’d fight!
He wants me to be afraid.
that’s obvious.
But the question is,
how’s he gonna do it?
I’ve gotta find out.
Huh? What the--
what’s this piece of paper
stuck in the door?
( Sniffs )
( Grunts )
He’s underestimating me again,
but, based on this scent,
i’m sure the paper is a trap,
and i’ve figured out
what kind it is, too.
I’m opening the door,
highway go go.
This guy can turn fire
into paper, too?
I’ve seen through
your little trick.
josuke, koichi,
i’m gonna get you out of there.
But unless my nose
is lying to me,
there’s something else lurking
in there besides those two.
( Sighs ) Wait.
I’m gonna have to go about this
very carefully.
( Sniffs ) How strange.
It’s like that other smell
is moving around.
It’s faint, but I think
it’s coming from...
( Sniffs )
What?!
Crap! Highway go go!
( Gasps )
What the heck is this stuff?
wait! I think
it’s some kind of chemical!
Shit! One thing after another!
Wait a sec. What’s this?
Now i’m getting
a nose full of iron.
Okay, just calm down.
remember,
he wants me to be scared.
if I allow him
to freak me out, he wins.
Iron. What is it, a machine?
( Shuddering )
Screw this shit! I just
have to open the damn paper!
Josuke! Koichi!
( Screams )
This doesn’t make any sense!
How the hell can his stand
hide electricity in paper?!
And if this predicament
wasn’t bad enough,
i’m smelling that horrible
mechanical stench again!
But why?
( Gasps ) It’s a shredder!
♪
( Gasps )
It won’t turn off.
It’s pulling in
josuke and koichi!
Damn! Highway go go!
it’s no use.
Highway go go’s too weak!
It’s not capable
of stopping this thing!
( Yells )
No! Josuke! Koichi!
terunosuke: So you
finally gave in, yuya fungami,
the onset of fear,
followed by a touch to the chin,
though fear
just isn’t your look.
( Yuya gasps )
terunosuke: Scaring
the ever-loving shit out of you
was surprisingly simple,
yuya fungami!
misterioso
can turn absolutely anyone
into a piece of paper,
anyone, any time!
( Yuya laughs ) Really?
That’s what makes
your stand so amazing?
It instantly transforms
its target into paper!
( Terunosuke gasps )
Yuya: Isn’t that great?!
Yuya: I admit it. You win.
You really got me there.
Although, I couldn’t
be happier to lose.
After all, if I wasn’t
a flimsy piece of paper,
i wouldn’t be able
to reach inside the shredder!
Terunosuke: Wait! What did
you just pull out of there?!
You better not unfold
that sheet of paper!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Yuya: Totally worth it.
I’d turn into paper any day
to see that look on your face.
Josuke: Yuya fungami.
Well, damn, after that,
I gotta say you’re a cooler dude
than I took you for.
Terunosuke: Josuke higashikata.
Koichi hirose.
♪
( Gasps )
You stay the hell away from me,
or else i’ll take this paper,
and i’ll rip it to pieces!
Would you really sacrifice
yuya fungami like that?!
( Groans )
Reverb: Act three! Three freeze!
Terunosuke: This pressure.
Josuke: I’m trying to remember
what I said earlier.
I know i’m forgetting something,
but I don’t know what it is.
Oh, yeah. It’s coming back.
I think I said i’d kill you
when I got out of there.
yep, that is
definitely what I said.
( Terunosuke gasping )
josuke: Oh, yeah,
I think I also said something
about never forgiving
someone as vile as you,
someone who takes hostages,
someone who uses psychological
blackmail to screw with someone.
( Terunosuke whimpers )
Let’s just take a beat.
All I wanted to do
was observe people’s reaction
to fear stimuli! I swear!
I just acquired my stand
a bit ago,
so I guess I got carried away.
I’m so sorry for my actions!
- I feel like an absolute heel!
- Josuke: You know what?
I’ve actually noticed
something about you.
Terunosuke: Huh?
Josuke: When you get scared,
i’m pretty sure one of your eyes
squints involuntarily.
I guess you could say
it’s a habit.
- ( Terunosuke whimpers )
- josuke: But...
when you’re
really losing your shit,
you close both your eyes.
( Terunosuke whimpering )
( Shining diamond yelling )
( Terunosuke screaming )
Josuke: So you like
observing people, huh?
Then, please,
knock yourself out.
But you’re gonna
keep your mouth shut
and behave yourself, understand?
( Terunosuke moans )
I-i’m a book.
Narrator: The young misterioso,
terunosuke miyamoto,
human book
and out of commission.
josuke never
bothered reading it,
but instead donated it
to the morioh library.
Mention misterioso
to any librarian,
and they’ll let you read it,
but borrowing it is forbidden.
Don’t be surprised
if you hear a faint voice
while perusing its pages.
josuke: Well,
that’s taken care of.
so why do I feel
like i’ve spoken too soon?
Koichi: At the very least,
this means we’ve gotten
one step closer
to capturing yoshikage Kira.
Josuke: Maybe, but we still
don’t have a single clue.
Yoshihiro: Damn it all!
They’re resilient
little crotch crawlers!
( Telephone line ringing )
Cheap trap: Calling your friends
for help isn’t going to work.
You have some photos
to burn now, yes?
( Telephone rings )
- Koichi: Huh?
- ( Ring )
jotaro: All right.
I’m heading out for a bit.
joseph: Hmm?
Where are you running off to?
jotaro: To go and find
our leads as soon as possible.
I’ll investigate where each
missing person was last seen.
No one can escape
from their innate personality
for very long.
He’ll make his move soon.
Hayato: I’ll catch him.
i’ll find proof
that he’s not my real dad.
I will.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪