♪
Kira: Unfortunately for me,
kosaku kawajiri’s shoes
are a little
on the large side.
To avert suspicion, I have
to gradually swap them out
with ones that actually fit.
Hmm?
♪
Hayato.
No goodbye for your dad?
- Have a good day at school.
- ( Door closes )
- ( Shinobu screams )
- Kira: What the...
Shinobu: Hurry!
something horrible
is lurking downstairs! Oh!
oh, honey,
it was utterly horrifying!
i thought
I was going to die!
( Chuckles ) That was scary,
but now I get to melt
into the rugged arms
of the man of my dreams.
I love you so much,
honey bunny!
( Kira gasping )
Shinobu: Please, you have to get
that strange cat
out of our basement!
Kira: Hmm? A cat?
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
shinobu: We were
out of mineral water,
so I thought i’d go down to
the basement to get some more.
That’s when I noticed
the window was open
and something fuzzy and plump
was sitting in the corner.
But instead of a creepy monster,
it turned out to be one of those
adorable British shorthairs!
Could you believe it?
It had perfect proportions,
and those gorgeous yellow eyes
and velvety bluish-gray fur
were to die for.
Well, aren’t you
just the cutest?
Now, how did you get in here?
- ( Claws scrape )
- Whoops. Bad idea.
♪
- ( Claws scrape )
- eh?
He must have come in
through the window.
He’s a cute little thing, but he
can’t stay down here forever.
If I don’t get him to scat, he
might pee on that potato sack.
Oh, and what if he has fleas?
Ah! All I have to do
is avoid eye contact
and approach nice and slow.
- ( Claws scrape )
- ( Gasps )
♪
I know what to do!
If I show him i’m not a threat,
i’m sure he’ll
let me get closer.
Look, Mr. Kitty.
I’m showing you my belly
and being submissive.
( Laughs ) Let’s be friends.
What do you say?
- ( Claws scrape )
- ( Gasps )
( Claws scrape )
( Sighs ) Hang on.
why am I begging
for this cat’s attention?
Time to scram, kitty.
you’ve more
than outstayed your welcome.
Don’t test me, cat.
( Cat yawns )
( Shinobu growls ) Screw you!
Eh? ( Growls )
( Cat purrs )
( Shinobu yells ) Enough!
- eh?
- ( Cat hisses )
( Shinobu yells )
He was hanging on the ceiling
like some kind of furry bug!
Kira: Hmm.
Shinobu: As terrifying
as that was,
it gets even scarier!
it’s crazy,
but when I saw its neck,
it had a gaping hole in it!
It was as big as a one-yen coin.
And then I heard something
come out of it!
( Hollow meow )
Kira: Really? A hole?
Curious.
Could it be a wound
from the arrow?
Shinobu: I swung the broom
at him like a madwoman
before he finally ran away.
please, can you
go down there and look around?
I’m scared out of my mind.
Kira: You said he had
a gash in his throat?
Shinobu: Well, dear,
what’s going on down here?
Is the cat gone?
( Kira sighs )
He is, dead and gone.
shinobu: Huh?
What are you talking about?
Are those...
kira: Shards of glass
that ripped through his body.
Shinobu: No, it can’t be!
I was just trying to--
Kira: It was an accident.
No one’s at fault.
Just bad luck.
( Shinobu sobbing )
Kira: No one did anything wrong,
least of all, you.
( Shinobu sobbing )
Kira: Apparently he had
a gash in his throat
before the accident,
but now there’s no telling
if he was a stand user.
no, he was
just an ordinary cat.
( Thunder crashes )
♪
Singers: ♪ morioh Cho radio
♪ morioh Cho radio
announcer:
With love, morioh Cho.
Kai: Good morning, morioh.
There’s nothing better
than the morning
after a heavy rain. Am I right?
I saw a beautiful rainbow
on my way to work.
I wonder if it’s still there.
( Flower squeals )
Narrator: "What is this place?"
He thought to himself.
"Why am I here? Meow, meow.
"Someone got me with an arrow
a couple of days ago,
"but I thought
I came out of that scrap okay.
"What?! My body is
totally different!
"This doesn’t make any sense.
"Why is it all weird now?!
And why the hell am
I stuck in the ground?"
he meowed
in panicked confusion.
( Door opens )
Shinobu: Where in the world
did he Bury him? Poor thing.
I’m so sorry, pretty kitty.
I hope you rest in peace.
narrator: "Hmm. Who is
this strange lady?" He wondered.
"i’m getting
a real bad feeling about her."
"The broom! Now I remember!
"This woman, she was there
"when all that glass
got stuck in me
"and I wasn’t able
to move anymore!
"I’m in this whole mess
because of that
horrible woman!" He fumed.
A flurry of confusion
overcame him.
( Shinobu gasps )
( Yelping )
( Flower squeals )
Narrator: "What was that?"
He thought.
"Something just happened. When I
let my anger for that lady out,
she fell over in pain."
shinobu: My toenail!
What the hell happened to it?!
Oh, no! It might be a curse!
Did I get it from that cat?!
( Whimpers )
( Birds chirping )
( Flower squeals )
Narrator: Having survived
his entire life
by using his animal instincts,
he intuitively understood
his new power and how to use it.
( Flower purring )
( Meows )
Kira: The little bastard’s
a stand user.
But why is this thing growing
where I buried
the stray cat last night?
And for that matter,
what the hell is it?
What did it do to that sparrow?
I didn’t catch a glimpse
of its stand.
more importantly,
I need to somehow figure out
whether this thing poses
a genuine threat to me.
doesn’t seem like it
wants me dead, but even so...
To be on the safe side,
i’ll have to prune it.
( Flower squeals )
( Yawns )
Kira: It fell asleep
eating its prey.
Is it a type of plant,
or could it be an animal?
Eliminating it would be easy,
so I have time
for a little investigation.
Psst, psst, psst.
( Flower hisses )
Kira: Hmm. The way it
innately looked back at me
when I called it
appeared almost catlike.
How strange.
( Flower chitters )
The way it seems compelled
to sniff my hand
is also uniquely feline.
It enjoys being petted as well.
( Flower purring )
Kira: Factoring that in
with its eerie purring,
it’s acting like a cat does
before it falls asleep.
But none of that tells me
whether it harbors
any ill will toward me.
I have to know for sure,
and there’s only one way.
( Flower snorting )
( Growling )
( Hisses )
kira: Well,
it’s certainly angry,
but, at the very least,
now I know
this thing doesn’t
want to do me any harm.
There’s no doubt. It’s the cat
I buried here yesterday.
So the gouge in its throat
was from the arrow.
What does it mean?
Shinobu: Um, honey?
( Kira gasps ) It’s her!
( Flower squeals )
( Shinobu gasps )
I wouldn’t stand in that spot
if I were you.
My toenail got ripped off
right over there.
It’s dangerous, dear.
Kira: I see. The cat
must have gotten angry
and attacked the woman.
If she ever found out
this thing existed...
( Swallows )
She’d run her big mouth,
and gossip
would eventually spread
to jotaro kujo and
his obnoxious cohorts.
I can’t allow that to happen.
Shinobu: What are you doing?
That’s where you
buried the cat, right?
I don’t like that spot.
It feels like it’s cursed.
Kira: I buried the cat
somewhere else.
Now please go back inside,
and nurse your foot.
Shinobu: No, you’re lying!
You’re lying to protect me
from something, aren’t you?
- ( Both gasp )
- ( Flower shrieks )
( Hisses )
kira: Shit.
It looks like I was wrong.
This cat is gonna be
nothing but trouble!
i may not know
what its stand can do,
but i’ll exterminate it
nonetheless.
Deadly queen!
Sorry, but you’re
about to be uprooted.
Bomb type one, switch on!
What the--
th-there’s no way
it could be a dud.
Which means this thing did it.
it must have
anti-detonation abilities.
( Flower hisses )
Shinobu: Huh? Is that a plant?
Wh-why is it moving?
Kira: Didn’t I just tell you
to go inside?!
Shinobu: Huh?
( Gags )
Kira: Shinobu!
( Flower grunts )
( Hisses )
( Kira gasps )
The moment that cat-plant
batted away deadly queen’s bomb,
it exploded!
Could this thing’s ability be...
Narrator: As the creature saw
the woman lying unconscious,
it thought,
"i’m going to kill her!"
Kira: That’s quite enough.
Your attacks on her end now.
- You’re about to disappear.
- ( Flower screeches )
Narrator: "If he wants to get
in the way, then he dies, too!"
kira: There’s
no other explanation.
The bomb failed to explode,
because it was deprived of air.
Narrator: The plant
instinctively knew
how best to utilize
its newly acquired abilities
to kill its enemies.
Kira: Wait a minute.
Could its stand ability be
to control the air around it?
It’s coming. It fired something,
but I couldn’t see what.
Deadly queen!
So it did shoot at us.
the little shit,
it’s weaponizing masses of air!
deadly queen: Bastard!
I’ll pound you into fertilizer!
What?! It’s like i’m pressing
on an invisible balloon.
kira: It really
can manipulate the air.
What?! ( Groans )
( Flower growling )
( Kira gasps ) Damn it.
( Gasps ) I can’t see it,
but it must have released
another one of those
compressed air bullets.
but where did
that creature aim it?
What?! It hit the cactus!
Shinobu!
( Flower growls )
( Purring )
♪
Kira: This doesn’t
make any sense.
Did yoshikage Kira just feel
a sense of relief for this woman
because the cactus needles
missed her eyes?
What is this feeling?
Could I actually be worried
about someone else?
What am I thinking?
My only concern
is what might happen
if this woman dies
and jotaro kujo discovers
i’m at this house.
That’s the only reason
i’m relieved to see
that she’s safe.
That’s all there is to it.
Your air attack
is now powerless.
Your projectiles
might be invisible,
but I know
how your tricks work.
You simply compress air
and launch it at your opponent
in a scattering of projectiles.
now deadly queen knows
how to get around your attack.
( Flower meows )
( Purrs )
Kira: Hmm?
What? ( Gasps )
The little shit! He injected
an air bubble into my vein!
( Grunts ) It’s traveling
deeper into my body.
I’m not exactly
a medical expert,
but injecting more than 10 ccs
of any gas into a vein
can cause blood vessel blockage
and death.
and i’m positive
this is way more than 10ccs!
No!
Damn, I can’t get it out!
There’s no other way.
I have to do it!
Deadly queen!
( Groans )
I underestimated
that wretched weed.
Its power to control
and attack with air,
it’s more formidable
than I imagined.
What do I do?
all right,
it’s preparing to fire again.
Think!
( Flower meowing )
Kira: That was far too close.
i suppose
i’ll let it slide for now.
Its execution has been stayed.
Shinobu: Kosaku told me
that he buried that poor kitty
far away from the house.
When I told him
about the cat’s curse,
he said it was just
a figment of my imagination
brought on by fear
and that I should get some rest.
I can’t believe it.
I fainted right in front of him.
How embarrassing.
but he was nice enough
to stay home and look after me,
even though it made him
late for work.
It was like a dream.
It felt like he understood me
for the first time ever.
This has been the most blissful
morning of my life.
♪
Well, are you enjoying it?
( Door closes )
( Front door closes )
Shinobu: Really, hayato?
I can’t believe
that boy left home
without saying goodbye again.
Kira: That little brat.
Has he been watching me?
- Shinobu: Oh, no, sweetie!
- Kira: Hmm?
Shinobu: You’re eating
from my plate.
I know how you hate shiitake
mushrooms, so I took them out.
what brought about
this sudden change of heart?
- ( Kira gasps )
- Shinobu: Wow,
you’ve already eaten
more than half of mine.
( Laughs )
But don’t get me wrong.
I’m positively thrilled
to see you wolfing them down.
They’re not so bad when you
give them a chance, are they?
Kira: Yeah.
All right, then.
I’m heading out.
Shinobu: I hope you have
a good day, sweetie pie.
( Sighs )
( Sighing )
( Door opens )
- ( Door closes )
- eh?
( Sighs )
Aww. That’s too bad.
A goodbye kiss
would have been nice.
Although, I feel as though
we’re closer than ever,
and before long,
my seductive love
will overwhelm him.
Hayato: He put his shoes on
with a shoehorn,
and he was definitely wearing
25.5-centimeter-sized shoes.
Why does he have shoes
that are two different sizes?
Even weirder, mom and dad are
getting along better than ever,
and he scarfed down
those mushrooms
even though he hates them.
Hmph. This is also bizarre.
why in the world
would he need to practice
writing his name
over and over again?
And then there’s what
I saw happen last night.
( Tape scans )
I kept replaying the footage,
but that’s just a pot of dirt.
What could he be doing
with that much soil
and a bag of cat food?
Then he goes into the closet
like everything’s normal.
♪
Hmm.
Eh?
( Children laugh )
Kira: They’re all wearing hats.
is that part
of their dress code?
What is this?
I’m getting a strange feeling.
Hayato: The attic.
Hmm?
Whoa. Oh, man, that’s weird.
I wonder what that thing is.
Freaky.
It’s way too dark in here.
I can’t make it out.
Kira: Hmm?
Hayato: There. It’s that bag.
- ( Flower rustling )
- huh?
Wha--
that plant is moving.
No, that’s not a plant.
It has eyes, and it’s
looking right at me!
Hang on! Could that bag of
cat food be for this creature?
Shinobu: I didn’t expect you
back so soon, honey.
Did you forget something? Ooh!
Did you realize you left without
giving me a goodbye kiss?
Kira: No.
Shinobu: Aww. Then what is it?
I can get it for you
if you want.
Kira: No. I’ll do it myself.
Hayato: Why the heck
did he come back?
( Gasps ) Oh, no!
- ( Flower meows )
- Hayato: Huh?!
♪
Guh! What did
this plant do to me?
( Groans ) What are
these weird things on me?
It’s like i’m being strangled
by some kind of invisible,
inflatable shackles.
i’m being pinned
to the air by the air itself.
( Stairs creaking )
He’s coming up the stairs.
I’ve gotta get free.
( Flower purrs )
Hayato: Huh?
( Yelps )
Kira: That came from the attic.
I knew that brat
was up to something!
Hayato: It hauled off
and attacked me
when I tried
to shut the window.
does that mean
it needs sunlight to move?
That’s it!
If i’m being held
by masses of air...
♪
Awesome. So the sunlight
was fueling it.
( Kira sighs )
That noise.
What’s going on here?
did the feral cat try
to get its food from the shelf
and end up spilling it
on the floor?
I thought the lack of sunlight
would keep it calm
for the time being,
but traces of light are
seeping in through the window.
Still,
I thought hayato may have
rummaged around up here,
but I guess I could
chalk that up to overthinking.
That said, had that little brat
discovered the truth
about who I really am,
then I would have had no choice
but to put an end to his life.
♪
( Hayato gasping )
Somehow he’s wearing
my dad’s face,
but that’s not my dad.
Who is that guy?
Wh-why is he here?
What does he want?
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪