Kai: Hello again.
You’re listening
to morioh radio,
and we’ve got
another rousing segment
for your aural pleasure,
"help! Midnight mentor."
Our first letter
is coming to you
from "forever 21, pretty baby."
"Kai, get a load of this.
Once again,
I was late
to my little rendezvous
because of that thing.
You know the one.
Exactly,
the one by the station,
the crossing that never opens
when you need it to.
It just goes ding, ding..."
- ( Listener sighs )
Whoa. Tell me how you
really feel, pretty baby.
( Listener groans )
♪
( Overlapping chatter )
Josuke: You serious?
( Koichi grunts )
Josuke: So I guess we aren’t
the only stand users
at this school after all, huh?
Tamami: Right.
Toshikazu hazamada,
enrolled as a junior
in group-c.
Apparently, he and his buddy
had a falling-out
over something trivial right
before the spring term started.
Seems the friend dissed
hazamada’s favorite idol
or anime or something.
Normally, that’d be nothing
to write home about,
but everything changed one night
when the friend
he was arguing with
gouged out his own eye
with a mechanical pencil.
( Koichi gasps )
Tamami: It’s crazy, right?
I hear hazamada’s friend
said this in the hospital,
"when I came to, I was staring
at my eyeball in my hand
with the only eye I had left."
( Koichi shudders )
Josuke: So you’re
saying this guy
ripped out his friend’s eye,
and he used some kind
of stand to do the job?
Tamami: Well, that could be
what happened here,
but there’s
no surefire way to find out.
Remember, the average person
isn’t able to see a stand.
Josuke: Yeah, I don’t know.
This all sounds fishy to me.
Tamami: What did you just say?!
Josuke, I don’t know
who you think you are,
but you’ve got no right
to say that to me!
I’ve got a real job now,
you know!
Koichi: Hang on.
You’re actually working now?
( Tamami chuckles )
’course I am.
I managed to land myself
a sweet little gig in finance.
Koichi: Finance, huh?
You sure that isn’t code
for loan shark or something?
Tamami: For now, let’s just say
i’m working
with some good people.
Josuke: That’s great,
but did you forget about this?
We’ve got work to do.
Koichi: Wait up, josuke.
Tamami: Master koichi,
you’re seriously gonna go, too?
Just let that jackass josuke
handle it.
Koichi: I have to do this.
Something evil’s
taking over our town.
And if morioh’s in danger,
then my mom, dad, sis,
and pretty much
everyone else I care about
are in danger as well.
I’m scared,
but it has to be done.
Tamami: Wow.
What a gutsy thing to say.
Then again, I would expect
nothing less from my hero.
But still...
You guys’ll have to excuse me,
as i’ve gotta get home now.
Stay out of trouble,
master koichi!
( Cash register dings )
♪
- ( Boy laughs )
- Boy #2: You guys
catch the game?
( Overlapping chatter )
Koichi: It doesn’t look like
he’s hiding out in this room.
Josuke: Honestly, it’d be
kinda creepy if he was in here,
him coming back to school and
acting like nothing happened,
especially after digging out
his friend’s eye with a pencil.
( Koichi sighs )
Josuke: Guys like that
are psychos.
Koichi: Hey, josuke,
what are you doing?!
Josuke: I’m just taking a quick
look through this guy’s locker.
- Keep an eye out, koichi.
- Koichi: The least you could do
is give me
some warning next time.
Josuke: All right.
He left his bag.
So he did come back to school.
Looks like he’s in
the tennis club and a manga fan.
( Grunts )
And he’d be right at home
in a hoarders club.
I don’t see how
he could have hidden
that bow and arrow in here
with all this shit.
Huh? The hell is
this wooden thing?
( Gasps )
A Stan--wait, no.
Looks like it’s
just an ordinary object.
Why would this freak have
one of those wooden mannequins
they sell in art stores?
That scared
the crap out of me.
( Creaking )
( Gasps )
Koichi: Huh?
♪
What? H-how?!
Josuke: I touched it,
and the thing turned into me.
Well, I guess
that pretty much proves it.
Hazamada’s a stand user.
( Robot chuckles )
Josuke: That’s just great.
Turning into me,
quite the cheeky move, pal.
Robot: The manga, "perman,"
you know it?
Koichi: I-it can speak! And it
sounds just like you, josuke.
Robot: If you read "perman,"
you’d know.
There’s a copy robot in it.
It’s handy, don’t you think?
I bet you wish that you
had one right about now.
Josuke: Huh? Hey, koichi,
what’s this guy mumbling about?
Who is this perman guy?
Robot: You’re telling me
you haven’t read "perman"?!
How’s that even possible?
Are you sure you’re Japanese?
That’s enough! I’ll be asking
the questions around here!
He’s got my arm!
Koichi: Josuke, no!
( Robot laughs ) However,
I must give you
a fair warning.
My robot is one that
you won’t want to have around.
( Josuke gasps )
Robot: Once it copies you,
you’ll be making
all the same movements it does,
which means,
it’s really not a puppet.
It’s actually a puppet master!
Josuke: K-koichi! Watch out!
( Koichi gags )
( Josuke gasps )
Robot: Hmm.
( Koichi gagging )
Josuke: Koichi.
Robot: Just like that,
another one bites the dust.
Best part, I didn’t touch him.
The honor of knocking him
into kingdom come
goes to you, his dear friend.
Josuke: It’s underhanded shit
like that
that really gets
my blood boiling,
making others
do your dirty work
’cause you don’t have
the balls to come out
and take care
of things yourself.
Nothing makes me want
to kick someone’s ass more!
Robot: That’s just great.
- Shining diamond: Dora!
- ( Robot scoffs )
- ( Josuke groans )
- Robot: It seems as though
i’m outside of your range,
and if you can’t
get any closer to me,
then neither can your stand.
In other words, josuke,
as long as I make sure
to always keep a little
distance between the two of us,
you don’t have a snowball’s
chance in hell of defeating me!
Shining diamond: Dora!
( Josuke gasps )
Robot: So you know,
my stand’s name is show off,
and possessing this doll has
given my stand physical form.
As a result, it can now be seen
by any ordinary person.
Josuke: Damn you, hazamada!
Show off:
My objective is simple,
pulverize jotaro
to within an inch of his life
and make sure
he never returns to this town.
( Josuke gasps )
Show off: He’s just
a pathetic outsider
snooping around
and getting in our business.
Although,
a little birdie told me
that jotaro’s star platinum
can stop time
for a couple of seconds.
There’s not a single
stand user among us
who can get
anywhere close to him.
Actually, the one stand
that can do the job
is the one that just copied you!
( Josuke gasping )
Show off: I’m taking you
out of the game,
but i’ll be sure
to give jotaro your regards!
( Josuke yells )
♪
Hazamada: The sound
of painful squishing,
it’s so sublime,
but as long as you
didn’t sever the nerve,
you might have a chance
at seeing again,
that is, if luck decides
to smile on you.
Show off: Given his injury,
I think
he’ll be out for a while.
Well, that was easy.
Hazamada: Hey, pick up my bag.
It’s time to start
our hunt for jotaro.
Show off: You made it too easy.
Now, if i’m not mistaken,
jotaro’s hotel is--
it’s the, uh...
Hazamada:
The morioh grand hotel.
Show off: Oh, yeah, that’s it.
( Reverb panting )
( Josuke groans )
Koichi! Koichi!
( Koichi gasping )
Josuke, what happened?
You’re not hurt, are you?
Josuke: No. I’m doing okay.
And you’re tougher than anyone
gives you credit for.
Even though
you’re all busted up,
you still managed to tag
that imposter with your stand.
( Koichi sighs )
What do you mean?
I was only able to do that
because of you.
The moment you sent me flying,
you healed my broken bones
with shining diamond’s power.
( Josuke chuckles )
- Koichi: But, uh...
- Josuke: Huh?
Koichi: Do you think you
could heal the injuries I got
when I slammed
into the door?
I don’t wanna be a bother,
but i’m in a lot of pain.
Josuke: Mm? ( Chuckles )
You bet.
♪
( No audible dialogue )
( Phone line ringing )
( Josuke sighs )
Receptionist: You’ve reached
the morioh grand hotel.
Josuke: Yeah. Hi.
How’s it going?
I need jotaro kujo. He should
be staying in room 324.
Receptionist:
One moment, please.
- ( Hold music playing )
- ( Josuke sighs )
Koichi: Hurry up!
We have to tell Mr. Jotaro
about that stand
before it’s too late!
Receptionist:
Thank you for waiting.
Unfortunately, the line
for room 324 is busy.
You can try
calling again later.
- Josuke: It’s busy?
- Koichi: What?!
Josuke: Of course!
He must be talking to the copy.
This is just great.
It got to him first.
♪
Jotaro: You sure, josuke?
You’ve found proof
that there’s another stand user
at your school?
Show off: That, I have.
I’ll fill you in
at morioh station.
Let’s meet
at the square in front.
You can get there
in 15 minutes.
Jotaro: Understood.
See you in front
of the station in 15.
( Hazamada laughing )
Show off: Easy as pie.
( Door creaks )
( Telephone rings )
( Ring )
Josuke: Shit! No answer.
This is bad!
Koichi: He must have left then,
which means they
probably baited jotaro
to go and meet them somewhere.
Josuke: Damn! All we can do now
is go after the copy.
Koichi: What do we do?
I couldn’t tell you two apart
to save my life!
Josuke: Yeah. Stealing my face
is weird enough,
but what really
freaks me out are his fingers.
How often do you catch
a glimpse of your fingers
compared to your face?
I realized that stand had copied
me down to the fingerprints.
Tamami: Huh? Hey, josuke,
you’re back early.
Where’s master koichi?
H-hazamada? What the heck
are you doing here?
Hazamada: Tamami kobayashi, huh?
( Chuckles )
Show off: You have no idea
why we’re hanging out?
Come on. Give it a guess.
Tamami: I’m all guessed out.
Show off: So you don’t even
have one little theory?
Tamami: Nuh-uh.
Should I have one, sir?
Show off: Nah, you’re good.
Jotaro: Step on it.
Josuke: If we don’t hurry
and catch up with hazamada,
jotaro is done for!
♪
Koichi: We can’t let jotaro
meet up with the copy,
or it’ll be a total disaster.
Josuke: Yeah, but I haven’t
figured out a solution yet,
so for now,
all we can do is run.
( Tamami groans )
Girl: We’ll catch you later,
josuke!
- Girl #2: See you tomorrow!
- Girl #3: Yeah, take it easy!
( Hazamada grumbling )
Girl #4: See you, josuke!
Girl #5: Bye, josuke.
Have a good evening.
Hazamada: Why the hell are
these chattering schoolgirls
only saying goodbye to you?
No one ever says stuff
like that to me
when I leave school for the day.
( Groans )
But why should I care,
since every girl in this school
is butt ugly.
- Girl #6: Josuke...
- Show off: Eh?
Girl #6: Um,
could you read this?
( Hazamada groans )
Girl #6: Well, bye then.
Hazamada: Why are you
accepting notes from her?
Like it would do you any good.
( Growls ) God damn it.
What the hell makes a jerk
like you so special anyway?!
Show off: What’s your deal?
The show’s over now,
so let’s just move on.
Hazamada: Wha...
Show off:
Maybe you’ve forgotten,
but we don’t have time
to dillydally.
Hazamada: How dare
you speak to me that way?!
Ow! That hurt!
Show off: Punching a guy
made of wood
was bound to end badly.
That was pretty stupid of you.
Hazamada: Shut the hell up,
and quit crowdin’ me!
Damn it. He’s really
starting to get to me.
This always happens
with my stand.
Like when I copied my crush,
junko, the other day,
she morphed
into a complete bitch.
I couldn’t take it,
so the entire thing was a flop.
Is there no one halfway decent
on this miserable planet?
That damn josuke’ll get his,
but first I have to take care
of jotaro.
I’ll crush him into paste.
( Laughs )
This is gonna be good.
Man: Huh?
You’ve gotta be kidding!
That guy smudged my motorcycle!
Man #2: What a douche.
Man #1: Damn that dumb-ass
and his dirty fingers!
I’m going to kill him!
Man #2: Take it easy, man.
It was probably an accident,
you know? Besides...
Man #1: What? Do you think
I care if that asshole hears me?
Just look at how he’s walkin’.
Damn, it’s like watching
a dying cricket
on a death march.
( Man #2 laughs )
Man, that was a sick burn!
Good one, dude!
Man #1: Yeah? You think?
It was pretty funny.
( Men laughing )
( Hazamada growls )
( Man #2 yelps )
( Man #1 gasping )
Hazamada: That’s it, show off.
Hold him still
while I settle the score.
( Man #1 panting ) What the hell
are you doing, you freak?
Knock it off! ( Groans )
Hazamada: Now don’t worry
your pretty little head
about what i’m gonna do.
Just focus on relaxing,
and i’ll make sure
you never open that mouth again.
( Man #1 shudders ) No!
( Hazamada gasps )
( Man #1 groans )
Hazamada: A glass shard?
♪
( Koichi panting )
( Hazamada gasps )
Josuke higashikata?!
What the hell?!
Even the shrimp’s still alive.
Koichi: Hazamada!
Josuke: We finally caught up
to you and Pinocchio!
Hazamada: How soon we forget.
Come face to face with
my show off if you dare, josuke.
The moment you do,
you’ll instantly
be turned into a puppet.
Control him! Now, show off!
Koichi: Not so fast.
♪
( Both gasp )
Hazamada: Wh-what’s happening?!
Josuke:
You mean it isn’t obvious?
That glass shard
I chucked your way
wasn’t meant to take you out.
I threw it so that it would
reform into its original shape.
Show off:
You sliced off my right hand,
and it turned back into wood!
This isn’t good, hazamada!
Hazamada: Settle down!
Just pretend you’re resting
your hand in your pocket.
No one’s gonna know.
More importantly,
that bastard jotaro
should arrive at the station
any minute now.
As much as i’d like
to get rid of josuke,
we don’t have time to waste
tracking him down.
Show off:
H-hazamada, wait for me!
Josuke: I see.
So they’re meeting
in front of the station, huh?
Koichi: We have to get moving.
Those two
already have a head start,
not to mention the fact
that the road they just took
is the fastest way
to get to the station.
Josuke: Yeah,
you’re probably right,
but i’ve got a secret weapon
in tow, koichi.
Koichi: You do?
♪
Jotaro: So he’s not here yet.
I guess
he ran into some trouble.
Hazamada: What’s the word?
You see josuke anywhere?
Show off: Nope,
nowhere to be found.
There’s nothing
to worry about, though.
If I so much
as glance at him,
he’ll be turned
into my puppet in a flash.
( Chime beeping )
Hazamada: Huh?
Show off:
Hear that, hazamada?
A train’s coming.
( Hazamada groans )
It’s the crossing from hell.
Waiting’ll cost valuable time,
so let’s
cut through the station!
( Laughs )
Even if he catches up to us,
the train’ll stop him!
Take that!
Show off:
There’s one minute left,
and all signs point to us
making it
to the meeting spot first.
( Hazamada laughs )
I win!
Huh? What the...
( Gasps ) Look there!
It’s josuke
and that brat, koichi.
( Growls )
Why’s the crossing open?!
Will someone explain
what the hell’s going on?!
Show off: Hazamada, over there!
Hazamada: Damn it!
He tricked us!
What is that stand?!
( Chime beeping )
Josuke: Great, right? You make
the perfect secret weapon.
Thanks for the assist
back there, koichi.
( Koichi chuckles )
( Running footsteps )
Josuke: There he is!
Hey, jotaro, it’s me!
It’s josuke!
Jotaro: Huh? Hey.
Koichi: We made it in time!
Boy, we got hazamada good,
didn’t we, josuke?
Jotaro: Did something happen?
( No audible dialogue )
♪
( Hazamada growls )
Jotaro: A copy?
A stand that copied
your likeness
down to the fingerprints?
Josuke: Yeah, it’s crazy, right?
If he’d gotten to you
before me and koichi,
who knows
what would have happened?
Koichi: But at least
now we can relax a bit.
Josuke:
I severed its right hand,
so it ought to be easy
to tell us apart.
I had to think on my feet,
but figured that would be best.
- Now we play the waiting game.
- Jotaro: Got it.
Koichi: We weren’t
that far ahead,
so they should show up
pretty soon.
Jotaro: Right.
Josuke: Hmm? Huh?
What am I doing with this?
This doesn’t make sense.
Why would I take a pen
out of jotaro’s pocket?
( Gasps ) I-I can’t move.
It’s like my arm
is frozen in place.
( Gasps )
- ( Show off chuckles )
- ( Josuke gasps )
- ( Josuke chuckles )
- ( Show off stammers )
- ( Josuke stammers )
Wait.
The other side of the glass.
Shit. It’s him.
- ( Pen clicks )
- ( Josuke grunting )
Hazamada: Josuke higashikata...
Like it or not,
you’re gonna plunge that pen
into jotaro’s brain.
The blunt-force trauma
should kill him instantly.
After all, leaving him alive
isn’t really an option now,
is it? Your stand
would only heal him anyway.
( Growls )
It’s your fault!
Your meddling is
the cause of this, josuke!
I was only gonna beat jotaro up
and chase him out of town
before you involved yourself
in my business!
But now jotaro’s gonna die,
and it’ll be by your hand.
Live with that,
you uppity ass-hat!
( Josuke grunting )
♪
Do it!
Send him to hell, show off!
Josuke: J-jotaro.
- Man #1: Bastard!
- ( Hazamada gags )
- Josuke: Huh?
- Jotaro: Huh?
Is something the matter, josuke?
Josuke: Uh, no,
though, fortunately for me,
it looks like those biker dudes
finally tracked down hazamada.
- ( Wood creaks )
- ( Hazamada gasps )
Man #1: You’re just
where josuke said you’d be,
you piece of bug shit,
hiding out at the station
like the coward you are!
Man #2:
That josuke fella is swell.
He went out of his way
to treat our wounds,
even if I don’t totally
understand how he fixed ’em.
( Hazamada growls )
Man #1: You know
what time it is?
It’s time we paid you back
for the stunt you pulled.
Man #2: There’s something
out behind the bathroom,
and we’re dying to show you.
( Hazamada screams )
Josuke: I’m not gonna lie.
That stand can be
pretty scary if it copies you.
All right, time to send it
to the big workshop in the sky.
I’ll feel a lot better
once it’s destroyed.
( Shining diamond yelling )
Narrator: Meanwhile, tamami
was admitted to the hospital.
♪
Chili pepper: Hah!
What a self-destructive fool.
( Laughs )
You have my condolences.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪