( Wind blowing )
¶¶
monster: Long have I awaited
this moment, human filth.
With the subterranean
and deep sea kings gone,
the terror lizard clan
can at last reclaim
rulership of the earth!
Hmm?
Man: Now leading target
towards point bravo.
Man #2: Roger.
We are inbound and on schedule.
Worker: We'll be on top
of bravo very soon.
¶¶
Tornado: Hmph!
( singing in Japanese )
Monster: And who are you?
( Cell phone rings )
Tornado: Hello. What is it?
( Monster stammers )
Tornado: Huh?
What do you mean, come back?
Uhh! You're the one who said
some weirdo monster was
waking up and flew me out here!
Monster: Weirdo?
Tornado: Yeah, that's right.
Yeah. I was just about to start.
Ancient king:
I am the ancient king!
- As ruler of the dinosaurs...
- Tornado: Trouble?
So what? That is not my problem!
Hey, shut your snout!
Can't you see
I'm talking on the phone here?!
( Ancient king gasps )
Tornado: I am so tired of this.
I mean, who does he think he is?
Annoying.
Hmm?
Ancient king: Are you done?
Tornado: What's with the chin?
Trying to be scary?
Should I be
shaking in my boots?
Ancient king: Act brave
while you still can,
you annoying little runt!
( Tornado growls ) Who are you
calling a runt, you toad?!
( Ancient king roars )
Hmm?
Ah, so you aren't helpless.
But to destroy me,
a giant meteor
is about the only thing
that's strong enough.
Tornado: Fine.
I'll get one of those, then.
Ancient king:
Don't make me laugh.
( Roaring )
Uh...
( Explosion echoes )
Tornado: How about another
300-million-year nap?
Hmph!
( Tires squeal )
( Bird calling )
Bang: Fist of flowing water
crushing rock!
¶¶
it goes something like that.
Want to give it a try?
You're both strong
and look like quick learners,
I bet you'll get
the hang of it in no time.
What do you say?
Saitama: Is this
really the cool thing
you said you wanted to show us,
a sales pitch for your dojo?
Thanks, but I'll pass.
You can do it, genos.
Genos: No. I will pass as well.
What I seek to learn
is not the art of self-defense,
but total destructive power.
Student: You punks!
Mocking our fighting style?!
I, the top disciple,
charanko, challenge you!
I--i give up!
( Groans )
Genos: Is he really
your best student?
Bang: Hmm. Afraid so.
Genos: But I had heard
that your dojo
was brimming
with skilled fighters.
Bang: Hmm. Well, one of
my best disciples went wild.
He beat my most skilled
students so badly,
they're all
out of commission.
The rest got scared and quit.
Understandable,
but unfortunate.
Saitama:
Is he really that strong?
What's his name?
Bang: Garo.
¶¶
even though he was
my top disciple at the time,
I gave him a good beating
and expelled him.
Saitama: You must pack
a mean punch, old man.
Charanko: Hey, watch it!
This is
the famed hero silverfang,
class s, rank three!
He toys with opponents,
flowing like water,
then delivers a blow
like a raging river
smashing a Boulder!
A master of martial arts!
You only recently
became a hero, right?
That would explain
your ignorance.
You'll regret ever taking
master bang so lightly!
Bang: Enough, charanko.
Do not disgrace us so.
Our guest saitama is
many times stronger than I am.
Charanko: You can't
be serious, master.
- ( Door opens )
- Worker #2: Mr. Silverfang!
( Panting )
I was sent by the association.
An emergency summons has been
issued to all class-s heroes!
Please come
to association headquarters now!
Hey, wait. You're out here
as well, Mr. Genos?
Thank goodness. Perfect timing!
Since all class-s heroes have
been summoned, please come, too.
Genos: Has it reached
threat level dragon?
Bang: Here we go.
Charanko, look after the dojo.
Charanko: Be careful, master!
Genos: If all class s
are being summoned,
then they may need
your assistance as well, master.
Will you come with us?
Saitama: I will.
Nothing better to do.
¶¶
hero: Ah.
Hey, there, silverfang.
Bang: Atomic samurai.
It's been too long.
Atomic samurai:
I figured you'd be here today.
And this is
the cyborg genos and--
hold on. I don't recognize you.
Bang: This is
the class-b hero saitama.
His great talents
will surely place him
atop class s one day,
so we asked him to come.
Saitama: Oh, hey, there,
middle-aged hero dude.
Nice to meet you. Huh?
Atomic samurai:
No handshake for you.
I only acknowledge the strong.
But someday, once you've
climbed up to class s,
I'll greet you properly.
Besides,
I'm not middle-aged yet.
I'm only 37 years old.
Saitama: 37 isn't middle-aged?
I had no idea.
Tornado: Hey, who brought
a class-b nobody along?
Don't you think mingling with
the less-thans is beneath us?
And even if you were invited,
a polite person would decline.
( Scoffs ) The nerve.
You're probably just here to get
close to us class-s heroes.
You disgust me. Get lost.
Saitama: Uh...
What's with the attitude
from this lost child?
Genos: That is tornado,
class s, rank two.
Tornado: Hey, who're you
callin' a child, chrome dome?!
Genos: She is able
to defeat monsters
with her psychic powers,
using e.S.P.
Saitama: Yeah?
Genos: It appears
everyone has arrived.
We should join them.
Tornado: Ahh! You jerk!
Stop ignoring me!
¶¶
( soft murmuring, smacking )
( Puri-puri prisoner thinking )
Maybe this will be
my chance
to get closer to genos.
Genos: It must be serious.
Almost all of class s is here.
Metal bat: Demon or dragon,
whatever, bring it on!
Tank-top master: Saitama?
That name rings a bell.
( Watchdog man sniffs )
Pretty sure somebody farted.
Blackluster: They're all
checking out my guns.
Boom! Hell, yeah!
( Whirs )
Zombieman: No one looks
particularly enthusiastic.
And does that pig
ever stop eating?
( Heart beating )
Child emperor:
Rank one's a no-show again?
I was hoping to see him.
Atomic samurai:
I still don't get it.
Is silverfang going to take
those youngsters on as students?
Bang: So why have we
all been gathered here?
Tornado:
Who really cares, anyway?
I had to drop
everything I was doing
and was kept waiting
for over two hours.
( Music stops )
Saitama: Can I have some tea?
Heroes: Huh?
Executive: My apologies.
I was delayed.
- We do not know...
- Saitama: Oh, thanks.
Executive: The whereabouts
of metal knight or blast,
nor can we reach them
at this time.
There's no sense
in waiting any longer,
so let's begin
this emergency meeting.
As for introductions,
you can call me sitch.
I represent the association
and will be briefing you.
So let's get right down
to brass tacks, shall we?
You heroes are here 'cause
you're the best of the best,
the top of the class. And now...
We're asking you to rise to
the occasion and save the earth!
However, I must warn you
that even with
your class-s skills,
there is no guarantee
of survival.
Walking away also takes courage.
Anybody choosing to do so now
will still retain
class-s status,
but those among you
who stay and hear me out
will not be allowed
to walk away from this briefing.
You will be confined here
until we are certain
the incident is over
in order to avoid
a general panic.
All right then, are all of you
willing to hear this?
Metal bat: Look, buddy.
Whatever's going on around here,
it better be worth
calling all of us.
I skipped out
on my little sister's
piano recital for this.
She'll be crushed.
If it's a total load of crap,
then I'm gonna tear
this whole building apart.
Tornado: Hmph!
Like you could do that
with that skinny stick, anyway.
Metal bat: Yeah?!
How 'bout I
bust your head open instead?!
Tornado:
If you think you can do it,
bring it on!
Stupid pill-bug head!
Metal bat: What'd you say?!
Flash: Just hurry up
and get on with it.
Otherwise, Mr. Pompadour
over here is going to die.
- ( Bat clatters )
- Metal bat: Hey, Bobby pin,
you siding with the girls?
What's your problem?
Sitch: The great seer known
as madame shibabawa is dead.
Zombieman:
Wait. Madame shibabawa?
- Was she murdered?
- Worker #1: No.
While looking into the future
for the next six months,
she became agitated
and had a bad coughing fit.
She popped a cough drop in her
mouth to ease her discomfort
and unfortunately
ended up choking on it.
Blackluster: I get it.
So we have to figure out
some way to prevent disasters
without the help of predictions.
That's the reason we were
all called to this meeting.
Sitch: Incorrect.
Madame shibabawa
has only been able to predict
a handful of disasters
over the years.
- Saitama: Excuse me.
- Sitch: The truth is...
Saitama: Hey, you there.
Puri-puri prisoner: Huh?
Saitama: Who is
this shibabawa, a hero?
Puri-puri prisoner:
You haven't heard of her?
She's a seer,
a great one at that.
She correctly predicted
earthquakes
and monster attacks.
Supervisor: We've gotten
through many crises
without madame shibabawa's
predictions.
Still, we provided her
with a bodyguard
and gave her special treatment
for her services.
Sitch: Indeed,
and that's because
her few predictions
were 100% accurate.
The crux of the problem,
though, is this:
I hold in my hand her last
and perhaps greatest prophecy.
As she took her last breaths
choking on that cough drop,
she managed to leave this note.
It is a grave prediction that
will absolutely come to pass.
Here it is!
Can you read it?
Heroes: "Th-the earth is...
In trouble"?!
Child emperor: Are you kidding?
That is so dumb.
Can I go now?
I have cram school.
Sitch: I know you're a prodigy,
child emperor,
but if you cannot grasp
the catastrophic danger
I've presented before you today,
it reveals
just how immature you are.
Child emperor:
What'd you say?!
Sitch: Now calm down.
Everyone, listen up.
Madame shibabawa's predictions
are 100% accurate.
She's miraculously foretold
numerous tragedies
and disasters in the past.
While many were saved,
a few of them resulted
in the loss of countless lives.
But not once
in all of her predictions
did madame shibabawa use a word
with the same weight
as "trouble."
Something more dangerous
than a dragon-level cataclysm
or monster is on its way.
Of that, we can be sure,
and it will occur
sometime in the next six months!
( Heart beating )
Watchdog man:
Okay, but does that mean
you have no idea when
in the next six months?
Flash: Yeah. It's kind of hard
to plan for that.
Sitch: Yes,
your observations are correct.
But I want you all
to be ready for a fight
in the next six months.
Is that understood?
Saitama: In the next six months
means that it could be
tomorrow or even today.
Sitch: Uh, yes, that's true.
Who are you, anyway?
( Saitama chuckles )
It's a good thing I came.
( Rumble )
( Heroes gasping )
Genos: The building
is under attack!
Blackluster: Wait.
That's impossible.
This is the hero association
headquarters.
( Crowd screaming )
( Monster laughs )
That's quite the formidable
fortress, to be sure.
( Laughs )
Time to attack!
Hawk, eagle, falcon, and kite!
Monsters: Yar!
Leader: Wipe out
these so-called heroes,
and the land below
will belong to us!
We will dive in headfirst.
Follow me, the sky king!
Fly!
- Soldier: Father, above us.
- Sky king: Eh?
- Soldier: Fly away. ( Gags )
- ( Soldiers squawking )
Sky king: The sky king,
killed like
some worthless little insect.
Who could have--uhh!
Monster: What was that?
( Monster #2 identical )
Who knows?
( Monster #3 identical )
It flew, so we killed it.
Head #4: That is good.
Head #5: Duty,
to protect the ship.
¶¶
( rumble )
Ated.
Sitch: What in blazes was that?
What in the hell is
going on out there?
Supervisor: I don't know, sir!
All communications
have been cut off.
We're in the dark!
( Sitch groans )
I-Impossible!
( Child gasping, coughing )
Dad!
Father: We're okay now, son.
Grab on to me.
There you go, that's the way!
That's it. Good job!
( Boy crying )
Eh?
¶¶
( shudders )
Monster: What is this?
It appears there are survivors.
Head #5: The ship
failed to kill them all.
- Head #3: We won't.
- Head #5 that is good.
Hero: Get away from here
right now!
( Gasps )
Hero: You think I don't sense
your thirst for blood?
I accompanied master atomic here
and was waiting
for the class-s meeting
to come to an end,
only to meet
thunder and destruction.
Is this your doing, beast?!
Sitch: D-destruction levels
are at 99.8%?
City a has been leveled!
It was destroyed in an instant!
I thought we'd have more time!
How could we have known
her prediction
would come true so soon?!
Bang: Hold on. Why was
this building spared, then?
Worker #1: Metal knight
was given the assignment
to construct this building.
His cutting-edge specs
are why it's stronger
than the average shelter.
Metal bat: Ah, so that's
why there are no windows.
Child emperor:
We should go outside
and see what's going on
for ourselves,
just to be sure
the prophecy's happening.
Saitama: Master, will you--
master.
¶¶
saitama: That's big.
Are they aliens?
Oh.
So that's what blew
the city to pieces.
I've had enough.
Get lost!
( Hero panting )
Head #1: This is
one militant creature.
Head #2: Also cautious.
Head #3: Hurry.
Let us hurry and kill.
Head #4: That is good.
Hero: Can it even be destroyed?
Each of its strikes is lethal.
I can't beat this thing.
Head #1: Such a weak
and frail species.
Head #3: So easily killed.
Head #4: That is good.
Hero: It's splitting?
Damn it. What is this?
Monster #1:
I will dispose of this one.
You handle the others.
Monster #2: Very well then.
Monster #3: I will go kill
those that ran away from us.
- Monster #4: That is good.
- Monster #5: I--
hero: Master!
Atomic samurai:
Iairon. You don't look so good.
You okay?
Your left arm's kinda--
iairon: Master!
Swords have no effect
on this strange creature!
Forget about me!
Get out of here!
Atomic samurai: Begone!
Iai, the path of the sword
does not end for you yet.
Stop bleeding!
( Iairon gasps ) Yes, master!
( Monster laughs )
Good. Seems a life-form
on this planet can fight.
Excellent. I invite you to try
withstanding our invasion!
Atomic samurai: Planet, huh?
So you're
from outer space, then?
And you got friends in that
floaty-toy-ship thing, right?
( Alien grunts )
Atomic samurai:
Yeah, that's it.
I doubt you have
the strength or the power
to cause this much destruction
to the city by yourself.
Bang: You can count us in,
atomic samurai.
Metal bat: You the ugly bastard
that smashed this town?
Alien: Hah!
What happens if I say, "yes"?
Puri-puri prisoner: For all
the beautiful men you killed,
I claim vengeance!
( Roars )
( Thinking )
Like he said,
each separate attack
must be delivered with intent...
To kill!
Dark angel...
Flash!
( Roars )
( Alarm blaring )
Supervisor:
Issue an evacuation warning
to city a and all
neighboring cities right away!
Workers: Yes, sir!
Supervisor: And expand
the system-m vitals monitor
to cover all of city a.
We need an accurate count
of the survivors
we'll need to rescue.
Worker #3:
What's the threat level?
Worker #1: Dragon,
without doubt.
( Workers gasp )
Supervisor: Not quite.
This might be god.
Child emperor:
Four class-s heroes
can take care
of the enemy on the ground,
but the real problem's up there.
We can't reach that ship.
Any aircraft would be shot down
in a matter of seconds.
Blackluster: Any ideas?
You're one of the top fighters
in class s, king,
so I'd love
to hear your take on this.
Genos: King, class s, rank 7,
said to be
the strongest man on earth...
- ( Heart beating )
- And I see
that he is well respected
by the other heroes.
King: There's nothing
I can do here.
( Both gasp )
King: It's too high in the sky.
There's no way to attack it.
But the mysterious craft
is currently stationary.
We should use this opportunity
to call in metal knight.
Tornado: Are you kidding?!
How completely pathetic!
Aren't you supposed to be
the strongest man?
Blackluster:
Take it easy, tornado.
If you piss king off,
he will kill you.
Tornado: ...People have
been wiped off the planet,
and you're just going
to give them a free hand?
Unbelievable!
( Heart beating quickly)
Tornado: Well, forget it!
I'll just take care
of these creeps myself!
Genos: Wait. I will go, too.
I do not know
how effective I can be,
but I will attack
the enemy from the ground.
Tornado: Maybe you
didn't hear me.
I said forget about it, okay?!
Blackluster: Whoa!
Take it easy there, genos.
I know how you feel,
but if you piss her off,
she will kill you.
( Genos thinking ) Very well.
There is no need
to team up with others anyway.
Master has already successfully
boarded the enemy ship.
Whether this is
the prophecy or not,
there is not a single evil
that could defeat master.
If such an evil existed,
then I assume the human race
would have perished
into oblivion long ago.
¶¶
( alien #2 laughs )
Well done making it this far,
intruder,
but you have reached the end!
For I am groribas,
and there is no way
you can hope to defeat me!
My acid breath will melt you
into a pile of fleshy pulp!
Blehh!
¶¶
Saitama: Huh.
You'd think the boss would
have shown his face by now,
if he's even alive anymore.
¶¶
( singing in Japanese )