So have you finally
made up your mind, then?
No, I have not!
[USHIMATSU]
If you're staying,
your first job
is waiting for you,
so let's hurry up
and get you to work.
[motor running]
Good, right on time.
It's Chupakabura Manju.
With a brand new special design
to welcome our new queen.
I ordered one hundred
boxes to start with,
but, depending on
how fast they sell,
we might need to have
them whip up a few more.
Okay, sir, one thousand boxes.
That's the whole order.
Can I get you to sign
right here, please?
A thousand?
Why are you so surprised?
That's what you
told me to order!
I said a thousand manju!
There are ten in a box!
That means one hundred boxes!
What's wrong with you?
But you can't
even make a profit
off of such a tiny order!
Another problem is
it's a food order
and we can't return it.
So what do we do now?
Queen.
Oh, no.
[USHIMATSU] Your first trial
is going to be selling
every last one of these.
Wha--?!
Hang on just a second, here!
I need to tell you something.
I had a really good talk
with your wife last night,
and the truth is--
I came here without
knowing it was
a one-year contract, so I
wasn't prepared to move here--
[USHIMATSU groaning]
Oh! My aching head!
Here's what we're gonna do.
For now, your contract will last
until the manju
expiration date: one week.
One week's a good
compromise, right?
Yeah.
I guess I could do that.
Then, it's settled!
I promise to forget all about
that year-long contract
you signed if you can
sell all thousand boxes
in one week!
You've got a deal!
I'm gonna hold you to it!
And as soon as
the last one's sold,
I am on a train out of here!
[YOSHINO]
That was a dumb move.
I don't think I can sell
a thousand boxes,
at least not in a week.
Oh, sure you can!
I bet you'll be able to
get rid of the entire batch
of them in no time at all!
And really, if they don't sell,
they don't sell, you know?
Not the end of the world!
Kinda is.
Well, of course we'd
like to sell the manju.
And for your sake,
I hope we can.
Though it does seem unlikely
to get it done in a week.
[YOSHINO]
You know...
I'd rather not put my
faith in "unlikely" events,
so maybe let's come
up with a strategy--
May I ask who you are?
Don't you know? She told me
she was the manager here.
Haven't heard anything
'bout a manager.
Although, do I know
you from somewhere?
Oh! Oden Detective!
You're Maki from
The Oden Detective !
A detective?
No, it was a
really cool TV movie!
The Leisurely Case Files
of The Oden Detective !
You're an actor?!
She wasn't the
central character;
she played more
of a supporting role,
so most people don't know her,
but she's famous locally!
She'll always be "Maki from
The Oden Detective " here!
Whoa, then she'd be
way better at this job
than I could ever hope to be!
Please take my place as queen!
Nope, no thank you.
[MAKI]
These are not cute.
They're terrifying.
Seriously, what's a
Chupakabura, anyway?
Hmm... Your basic
mysterious monster.
Well, you cannot sell
ten thousand monster treats
in only a week.
But we have to try!
Like, what if we
convinced the store
at the train station
and the souvenir shops
to carry them?
Um, do you know
how many tourists
we get here in a year?
[YOSHINO]
Like, a hundred thousand?
Thirty thousand.
Not a lot.
Yeah, just a little
over five hundred a week.
Well, if we could
get each of them
to buy two boxes...
That would not
be normal at all.
Well, good, "normal" is boring!
[YOSHINO]
If tourists don't come through,
we'll get the residents
to buy them!
How many people live here?
[SHIORI]
Fifty thousand.
[YOSHINO] So if one
in fifty people buys one...
[SHIORI] That's a lot
to hope for, Yoshi.
Maybe it is, but I've gotta
believe I can sell all of them
and get back to Tokyo!
Here we go.
Our very first store.
[door opens]
Oh! It's the new queen!
You didn't go back
to Tokyo, I see.
Takamizawa.
He's one of the
local bus drivers.
Hello, sir.
--We met yesterday.
--[TAKAMIZAWA] We sure did.
Which lunch combo?
Ginger pork or curry?
Hi, Erika!
We didn't come for lunch;
we just need to
ask you for a favor.
[YOSHINO gasps]
One Fortune Teller Combo!
[SHIORI]
Huh?
[ANGELICA] Your human
strokes are very unlucky.
However, your heaven
strokes are good.
You will be blessed
in your golden years.
Yeah, I know.
So I've been told.
But how can I sell a thousand
boxes of these things?
That's impossible.
No, I have seen.
Wait, you've seen what?
Many things.
[YOSHINO]
Could you be more specific?
North by northwest.
Don't even worry about it;
her fortunes are
always like that.
We're heading in the
right direction, yeah?
[SHIORI]
You think it's for real?
Oh, it's a
Japanese sweets shop!
I bet they'll help us!
[SHIORI]
I doubt it.
They don't get along
with the tourism board,
and they're always
fighting with Mr. Kadota.
You old jackass.
Shut up, you stupid hag.
Great.
But you know what?
I bet Rii- chan might know
something about the Chupakabura.
Who's this "Rii- chan "?
A childhood friend.
She's just a little shy,
sometimes, that's all.
[SHIORI]
You there, Rii- chan ?
Oh! Hi there! Could we--
[SHIORI]
Wait a second, Rii- chan !
Open up!
So, listen.
Shiori tells me you might
know about the Chupakabura.
Can you explain it?
U.M.A.
U.M.A.?
An Unidentified
Mysterious Animal.
"Chupa" is the
Spanish word for "suck"
and "cabra" means "goat,"
so it literally means a creature
that sucks the blood of goats.
The earliest sighting was
in 1995 in Puerto Rico.
There have also been
sightings in Chile, Mexico,
and America,
however, no sightings
have ever been
reported in Japan.
The sighting here in Manoyama
was most likely a weasel.
I knew you'd
be able to help us!
Thank you!
[SHIORI]
She knows a ton about the occult
and things like that!
Pretty handy, huh?
Yeah, for sure.
I think we should really
push the occult theme
in the town's marketing!
And we need to create
a whole new website!
Uhh...
I don't know about
a new website
when the best I can do
is post photos to a blog.
[YOSHINO]
That's okay, who should I ask?
Well, we really
need to find a local
web designer to do it.
I remember there was
a woman that moved here
from Tokyo last year.
I'm pretty sure she
started up some sort of
web-related business, so...
Ah! Here it is!
Yes!
[YOSHINO]
Excuse me!
Hello? We're here with
the tourism board!
Maybe she's not home.
[SANAE] It's been six months
since I arrived in Manoyama.
The long winter has at
last given way to spring.
It's finally time to
fully enjoy the benefits
of a natural lifestyle here.
Today, some locals
gave me some vegetables,
so I used them to try out
this new radish dish.
With the breath of spring,
all the little bugs
have woken up hungry.
So perhaps the thing I should do
with all this bounty is share.
Hm?
[SANAE screaming]
[gasping]
--[SANAE screams]
--[SHIORI, YOSHINO gasp]
--[SANAE gasps]
--[YOSHINO] Are you okay?
Hold on, who are you?
[YOSHINO]
Are you hurt?
Tell me!
[YOSHINO]
Your headphones!
So sorry to barge in!
We're with the tourism board
and we really need your help.
[SANAE]
The tourism board?
What was that screaming about?
[SANAE]
Oh. That?
It was nothing, really.
I'm just fine.
I kicked the corner
of my armoire.
It's lovely living
in the country!
There aren't any armoires
in the city, you know!
Well, that might not be true,
but I never kicked them there!
I swear, only out here in
the country, for some reason.
I mean, am I right?
[SANAE, YOSHINO scream]
[BOTH whimpering]
[SANAE] It's a bug,
it's a bug, it's a bug!
[whimpering]
[SANAE]
I see.
I guess it's not easy
being the queen, is it?
Yeah, it's not what
I thought it would be.
Do you think you
can build a website
in two days?
I'm afraid we don't
have much of a budget
to speak of.
Aww.
Sure, I'll do it.
After all,
it's for the town, right?
Suppose I should help
them out if I'm able.
Thank you so much!
So, what kind of site
did you have in mind?
It's gotta go "boom,"
like, have major impact,
and it has to have an air
of the occult to it somehow
and also be fancy and cute.
And we need an online store!
There's no way I could
build an entire online store
for you in two days;
I would need at least a month
to set up the system.
A whole month, really?
Man, I was convinced
we could've sold
a thousand boxes online.
Maybe you should
try to think of it
the other way around.
[YOSHINO]
Which other way?
These days, you can
easily buy delicious food
from all over the country
just while sitting at home.
So if you emphasize the fact
that you can only get these
by coming here in person,
they'll seem more rare
and worth getting.
Exclusive.
But do you actually believe
that could work? Truly?
Oh, don't worry,
you just leave all that to me.
[screams]
Can we get out of here?
[SANAE]
Hmm...
This place is perfect.
I'll be able to get
tons of work done.
Here you are.
[SANAE]
Oh, thank you.
All right, why don't
we start by talking
some more about
the design you want.
Now, considering
the major time crunch,
we'll keep it as
simple as possible
while still maintaining
that bold feel.
You mentioned looking for a kind
of fancy occult vibe, right?
So how 'bout "Fancyccult"?
Yeah! Fancyccult!
How lovely!
Are you kidding me?
It'd be quite challenging
to come up with content
for a strictly occult
theme, so...
we'll push the subculture,
but keep it cute.
But I need something
for the copy. Hmm...
"A little treat from the
depths of the vampire forest."
Yes! That's it!
And there's lots of
wild garlic on the hill
behind our house!
So now we need to
look at text and photos.
Think you ladies could
help me out with that?
What's going on with you?
Nothing's going on.
That girl that just came by
is the new queen, right?
I wonder what that old man
is plotting over there.
Don't you get roped into
anything stupid, you hear?
[SHIORI] It looks abandoned
in these pictures.
Makes it feel occult-y.
You mean Fancyccult.
We can touch up the photos.
They'll be okay.
Isn't that deceptive?
No more so than
putting on makeup.
What are your thoughts
about the text?
Oh! Yes, here,
I underlined the parts
that I thought might be useful.
Thanks, that's great.
All right,
I'll get started, then.
Hey, thanks again, so much!
'Kay!
I guess we can go work on
getting the stand ready.
Let's go!
You coming, Maki?
Why ask me?
[SHIORI]
Hmm... This goes--
[gasps]
Let's see.
You're really
good at this, Maki!
I've done it on
my part-time jobs.
Oh, like to prepare for a role?
Don't I wish.
No, it's to pay my bills.
When you're an actor,
you have to take side jobs
in order to survive.
[YOSHINO grunts]
Hang in there, my queen.
The entire next year of my life
is riding on this.
If I wanna go home, I have
got to make this thing work!
Yoshino.
You really can't wait
to get out of here, huh?
[MAKI]
So...
What are you gonna
do when you get back?
What's waiting for
you there in Tokyo?
Uh, what's waiting there?
Everything's waiting there!
Tokyo is everything!
[YOSHINO] Maybe you should
take a little break
and get some sleep.
What do ya think?
I'm fine.
When I lived in Tokyo,
I would work through
the night on the regular.
Can you tell me something?
Why'd you leave Tokyo
to come live in this place?
[SANAE]
Hmm...
I kind of got tired
of the rat race.
Plus, nowadays,
there's no reason to force
yourself to work in a big city.
[YOSHINO]
But... I mean,
isn't Tokyo literally the
economic center of the country?
Yeah, that's a fact.
So there are more
opportunities there
than anywhere else!
What kind of
opportunities do you mean?
Well, there's...
anything and everything.
[SANAE]
What happened?
Couldn't find work?
Thirty-two applications
and not even one job offer.
Well, don't let it get to you.
You don't need Tokyo.
With the right mindset,
I believe you can
find work anywhere.
Just my two cents!
[YOSHINO sighs]
Wonder if she's right.
It's done.
[YOSHINO]
Fancyccult!
[SHIORI]
Oh, it's so adorable!
All that's left is
to post some links to it
on some other sites.
Okay, girls.
Now you're ready to go!
[YOSHINO]
How'd we not sell a single one?
Well, it is only
the first day.
Your journey has just begun!
I think it's more than that.
We're not getting nearly
enough traffic on the website.
[SANAE]
Huh?
What?
Seventy-six? Aww.
I wonder if Fancyccult
is too avant-garde
and freaky for people.
[YOSHINO] What I've been
wondering is how the heck
Mr. Kadota was planning
to sell all these manju
in the first place.
Apparently, his original plan
was to have that actress,
Yoshino Tsubaki, sell them
to people directly.
Yes, we can use that!
You can count me out!
My acting days
are long behind me.
[YOSHINO]
What? Me?
It makes perfect sense!
And you'll do great, Yoshi!
I guess, but I'm wondering...
It's the "beautiful queen"
part that I question.
Don't be silly.
I was totally planning to
touch up your photo, anyway.
That's not really
what I meant, though.
Is it more like you're
feeling weird and awkward
about being referred
to as "beautiful"?
Oh, okay, we'll
embrace that, then.
Little question mark
next to the word.
How about "relatively pretty"?
Thanks for that.
Just put, like, a little
asterisk right there
next to "beautiful."
Sure, great, but what's
the alternate word then?
[YOSHINO] "Buy them directly
from the hand of the beautiful
(based strictly on
individual opinion)
queen of our land."
I mean, at least
that's kind of funny.
Or, we could change
the whole concept.
Just lay it all out there.
"I ordered way too
many of these things.
Please help us out
and buy some."
--What do you think?
--Great.
Doesn't that make it
sound like it's all my fault?
[YOSHINO]
Yay!
How did it go?
Sold three boxes.
Met Shiori's whole family.
So it wasn't a total loss.
Yeah, my family
felt bad for us,
so they came out to buy a few.
That's all we sold?
Even after the queen
apologized for everything?
Well, she may
be the queen,
but nobody actually
knows who she is.
And I don't think
anyone is reading this.
Just for the record,
everything you say is negative!
I'm only doing this because
I want to help Manoyama.
Not for your own
self-satisfaction?
[SANAE gasps]
What is it you're
trying to say?
Come on, you guys,
we shouldn't fight each other.
I'm sorry.
Said too much.
Anyway, I tend to agree
that it's hard to connect
with words alone.
Hey, Maki...
You look like you have an idea.
Have you come up with something?
Yeah. I think a video
would have more impact.
A video.
[YOSHINO]
Sorry to drop in so late!
Evening there, my queen.
I heard you sold three
whole boxes today. Ha!
Just you wait.
It's not over yet!
[YOSHINO]
We got the costume!
[SANAE]
And the camera?
[SHIORI] Well, Rii- chan 's
got a really good one.
I texted her,
but she hasn't replied.
Guess she's not interested.
She's here!
I was able to sneak out.
The Oden Detective !
Please forget it.
You're a detective?
I said forget it!
Maki, thanks for doing this!
I did this kinda
thing part-time
on a superhero show.
You're right, you know.
Tokyo has everything,
and I did it all.
And anyway, making this
video was my idea.
Great attention
to detail, Rii- chan !
A chupacabra's skin has
to be moist to be correct.
And who're you, exactly?
Nobody. Random person.
[YOSHINO]
Okay, everyone!
Are we ready to do this?
And, action, go.
[MAKI growling]
[roars]
[gasp]
Oh, no! The Chupakabura!
Don't worry!
I'll take care of this!
[MAKI roaring]
[roaring continues]
[RIRIKO]
Cut. Take two.
[MAKI roaring]
[SANAE, SHIORI yell]
[SHIORI]
Oh, no! The Chupakabura!
Don't worry!
She freed the sword.
Mr. Kadota!
The queen freed
the sacred sword!
[MAKI roaring]
Ha!
[MAKI yelling]
The terrible,
vicious Chupakabura
is now the
delicious Chupakabura!
[MAKI] A little treat from the
depths of the vampire's forest:
Chupakabura Manju.
So delicious, it's fancyccult!
[YOSHINO sighs]
How are there
still no customers?
[harmonica music]
Look at that!
Manju are scary.
But I'll take one.
After all that work,
we still only sold one box.
Our video got a
fair amount of plays.
Maybe we should
all watch it again.
Or the "making of" short.
What? When did you
put that together?
[SANAE]
Oh, shoot!
We should have made that
an unlockable bonus video!
The expiration date
has officially passed.
So you failed
your first trial.
No worries, Yoshi!
[YOSHINO groans]
Hey, wait!
No, I say we eat them all!
They just expired, didn't they?
I'll take a pass. Thanks.
[MAKI]
There's no need to be neurotic.
It's okay, the date
is "best enjoyed by,"
not "must be consumed by."
Mr. Kadota said that we
were allowed to give away
whatever didn't
sell to commemorate
the coronation of the new queen.
Even though they're
already expired?
[MAKI] I told you,
don't be so neurotic.
These are actually really good.
All the ingredients come
from right here in Manoyama!
Hey, you're right.
They really are tasty.
I could eat ten more.
Really? At this hour?
You know, this is the
most fun I've had in a while.
Yeah, me too.
To be honest, you were the
first people I'd talked to
in, like, two weeks.
I was turning into a hermit.
I was even considering
moving back to Tokyo.
Hey! Why don't we all go
cherry blossom viewing?
It'll make for
a great wrap party.
[YOSHINO]
That sounds great!
The blossoms at
Cherry Blossom Pond
are supposed to be
gorgeous, right?
Hey, hold on.
Does that mean you're
not going back to Tokyo?
Because the cherry
blossoms won't even be
in full bloom for
another two weeks yet.
Oh.
Well, guess I'll stay till we
can see them together!
[SANDAL] In order to
save the desolate town,
our new queen has
freed the Sacred Sword.
Next time:
"The Cry of the Mandrake."