They were asking about
that, so tell the office.
Hello, can I
help you, gentlemen?
We're fine.
[SANAE]
Say cheese!
Okay!
The dragon play is
really coming along!
Way to go, you guys.
This will be posted on
the Manoyama channel.
Hey, Maki.
I understand that the dragon's
song is the theme here.
But, I don't think it's
a very good message.
Yeah, letting the dragon die
because of a misunderstanding
is a sad ending.
I know, I've been a little
concerned about that, too.
Some adjustments
might be a good idea.
[YOSHINO] I wish Manoyama
was this lively, don't you?
I don't know.
I kinda wonder why a
company in Tomikura
wants to help out with
the Mizuchi Festival.
Huh...
Oh. I think that's it!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm Kudo, the CEO here.
Did you notice the pastry
shop on the first floor?
I'm the one who runs it.
Oh! Right, it's called Belem!
It smelled incredible
when we passed by!
[KUDO]
You know, I really enjoyed
the school's Closing
Ceremony a few weeks ago.
Are you a graduate of
Manoyama Second Middle School?
I am!
And I heard that you're
trying to revive the festival
that used to be
held 50 years ago.
I'd love to help out with
that in whatever way I can.
Wow, thank you so much!
That's kind of you!
No, really,
the pleasure's all mine.
I felt like it was about
time to contribute
to my hometown if I could.
So, getting down to business.
Currently, we have two stores
in Tomikura and one in Tokyo.
And, now,
we're considering opening up
a new location in Manoyama.
Really? A new store?
[KUDO] Naturally,
we know the risk of opening
a business in a small town.
But, as I think we all realize,
unless someone does something,
Manoyama's decline
will continue.
The best case scenario
would be for someone
to rent a shop to us
in the shopping district.
Well, we'd love to help!
We can start asking
around for you.
[MINO]
This is delicious!
This isn't a typical
Manoyama egg tart, is it?
Nope, this is called a pastel
de nata and it's from Portugal.
[SANAE] Who knew Portuguese
desserts were so insanely good?
I can hardly believe
a pastry shop like this
would come to Manoyama!
Of course they would!
Obrigado !
[MINO] Still, you know that
if they want to join the
shopping district, we'll need to
go discuss it with Mrs. Oribe.
Yeah, I wonder what she'll say.
We still haven't even
received the official approval
from her regarding the festival.
She'll say yes.
Even that old hag couldn't
possibly turn this down.
Now let's go!
Gutsy, bringing a
proposal for a pastry shop
to a Japanese confectionary.
It's just, we thought
it was a great chance
to liven things up in
the shopping district.
They contacted the
tourism board about this.
If we hadn't held
that closing ceremony,
none of this would be happening.
That's a very
patronizing way to put it.
Look, all I'm saying is
that it's going to be good
for both sides.
[CHITOSE]
All right.
I've got to consider the
needs of the shopping district
ahead of my personal concerns.
I'll talk with the shop owners
whose stores have shut down.
Thank you... very much!
[CHITOSE]
By the way, old ass.
What do you want, hag?
I want to know what's going
on with the Mizuchi festival.
Whether or not the Board
of Merchants participates,
depends on your attitude.
You'd do well to remember that.
Okay, fine then, we'll go ahead
and include you officially.
Good enough, hag?
Show me some respect in my shop!
Go on!
'Scuse us, we'll be going.
[MAKI]
What is this? It's so good!
[SANAE]
I know, right?
That crispy crust,
with that thick, rich custard.
Oh! The contrast
is just amazing!
Even so, I'm blown away that
Chitose gave the okay for this.
She's always been very level
headed when it counts, though.
So Mr. Kadota's actually the
one with the screw loose, huh?
[laughs]
[SANAE]
Huh? Yoshino?
Huh?
What's wrong?
You seem out of it.
I realized there are only two
months left till the festival.
Once it's all over.
What the heck am I gonna
do with my life after that?
I mean, the queen contract
is for one year, right?
Shiori was already on the
Tourism Board when I got here,
Sanae, you have your work as a
web builder so you'll be okay.
Maki, you just started
an acting troupe.
And Riichan's family
has the confectionary.
I'm the only one with nothing.
What should I do?
How do you feel about it?
Are you considering
going back to Tokyo?
Oh, I don't know.
Even if I did, I might
not find anything there.
And I really like
it here in Manoyama.
Then why shouldn't you
just keep going as the queen?
It's not like Mr. Kadota's
letting you go.
I'm sure he'd figure
out something.
Yeah, maybe.
[SANAE]
Well, for now, we drink!
Girl, why do you
always have to do that?
[SANAE]
Do what?
I'm just brightening the mood!
Life is short so you
better drink up, little lady!
Maki, would you get some ice?
Jeez.
[CHITOSE]
So, that's a no?
Your place does have
separate entrances
for both the first and second
floors, isn't that right?
Right and it's not that
I mind renting the shop out.
It's just that I don't
think I can handle
that sickly sweet smell.
That burnt custard smell,
you know what I mean?
If that was wafting up 24 hours
a day, I think I'd... Ew!
That's okay.
I understand and I'm sorry
to bother you about it.
[IWASHITA] I tried a few places,
too, but it was no good.
None of them want
to rent out their shops
because they live
on the second floor.
I can definitely
understand how they feel.
I really thought someone
would be interested, though.
We've hit a pretty
substantial roadblock, here.
I'm honestly getting
a little worn out.
Come on, Chitose!
You can't possibly give up now.
[NUNOBE]
I agree!
[YOSHINO] Well, they haven't
been able to convince anyone.
There's still one possible place
they haven't tried yet, though.
The owner doesn't live
there anymore, either.
Oh, are you talking about
the old grocery store?
Maybe.
Is Belem Pastries really
coming to Manoyama?
Wait, how did you find out?
I would go there every day!
I mean, I could even work there!
Yeah, it's pretty
great news, huh, Erika?
If really are planning
to work there,
then it better be when
we're closed here, young lady!
Hey, it's not
exactly official yet,
so try to keep it
under wraps, okay?
[CHITOSE]
Hmm...
It's been quite
a while, Akiyama.
[SHIORI]
Here we are--
the old grocery store
Riichan mentioned earlier.
Oh, sure, Akiyama's shop.
He bought a place outside
town a while back.
He lives out there now.
Since nobody
lives on the property,
maybe he'll be
easier to convince!
And you know what else?
Akiyama already rented this shop
to an out-of-towner before,
a few years back.
If I remember,
the store sold accessories,
but they went out of
business pretty quickly,
Well then, seems
this is a great opportunity!
Yep! Right, because he might
be willing to rent it out again!
Okay!
Let's go talk to the
man ourselves, then.
Hang on, Mr. Kadota!
Hey, guys! Mind if we come in?
How's everything
been going in here?
Going well!
Thanks for asking.
I think we'll be able
to open up by next month.
So soon!
That why Sandal's helping too?
Is jazz fusion the
musical equivalent
of, like, Japanese fusion?
We're not talking
about cuisine, here.
Oh, hey. I wanted to read this.
Nice, the Shining Dragon.
I used it to wish for
success for my new business.
I thought, what could it hurt?
I wonder if it'll help at all.
I think miracles can happen
for those who believe.
Whatever you do,
what matters is how you feel.
Oh, they're back.
[USHIMATSU]
So, what do you think?
Good idea, right?
And now, a visit
from the Tourism Board.
No matter how many times
you ask, my answer is no.
Oh, come on, now, Akiyama.
It'd be for the whole town.
Don't you think it's kind
of a waste and a shame
for the town to keep
the store closed
while you're living
all the way out here?
No, I really don't.
What happens to that store
is my business, not yours.
Legally that is true, but at
this rate the shopping district
is going to die off, completely.
We're asking you.
Can you please
do this to help us
try to save the
shopping district?
Sorry, I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
Huh?
[SANAE] Aw... It seemed
like such a good set-up, too.
I can't imagine why
he would be against it.
Who knows. I wonder if he thinks
the district is beyond saving.
I have no doubt people would
want to come to Belem, though.
It's a big, fat waste.
[ERIKA] Are you guys
still going on about that?
If nobody else will
rent their place,
that's all the more reason
to take over this store!
Erika!
You're upsetting
your mother right now.
But I absolutely
must have pastel de nata !
I want it, I want it, I want it!
I'll make you some nata de coco.
You'll make do with that.
No!
It's obvious the town would
be better off with that shop,
but nobody's
doing anything about it!
That's why this place
a pit of despair!
And strike.
[MAKI]
Yeah, a fastball.
[RIRIKO]
It's my grandma.
She says the Board
of Merchants is holding
an emergency meeting,
and they would like
the Tourism Board
to attend if we can.
Meaning, us, too?
[MAKI]
Okay, today we'll be going over
the second half of the play.
I've added a final scene
in hopes of making
the folk tale theme
more easily understood.
Why don't we take it
from in front of the cave,
the part where
the villagers are parading.
[CHITOSE] I didn't call you all
here for this meeting in order
for us to talk about
the pastry shop.
I called you because
I thought it was time
we discuss the future of the
Manoyama Board of Merchants.
Undoubtedly, you are all aware
that Noge Books is planning
to open up a cafe soon
in the closed middle school.
Mr. Noge, how's it going?
Uh, well!
We got lucky in that the
school has plenty of parking,
and it's in a really
good location, too.
Interesting.
It's possible that area may be
the center of the town someday.
And, if that's what
comes to pass.
Then I think it would be time
for the Board of Merchants
to seriously
consider disbanding.
[gasps]
Are you kidding me?
I'm definitely not.
Nowadays, most people
buy their everyday goods
at the supermarket,
and many times,
it's easier to order things
you need off of the Internet.
Are you saying we
should just sit around
and wait for the town to die?
What choice do we have if
people keep closing their shops?
Why force ourselves
to keep going
if people don't
want to stay open?
Hold on.
Some of us here are nowhere
near ready to give up yet!
Please don't say you're
disbanding us now!
[USHIMATSU]
The wood-carving district
is still a viable
tourist destination!
It's the shopping district
that's the problem, right?
Yes. Throughout our history,
Manoyama has always
adjusted our business
to the changing times.
However, now the
very foundation of the way
we conduct our business
is quickly becoming obsolete.
On top of that, even if we
try to think of a new role
for the shopping district,
everyone here is old.
If we're no longer needed,
it's just a sign of the times.
All we can do is accept it.
I've taken over
my family's soba restaurant
and turned it into
a successful bistro.
We could have a
new generation of shops.
I believe that.
That's nice,
but my kid left for the city
and never comes back home.
Hold on, I don't understand
what there is to discuss here.
All we need to know is
that having Belem Pastries
come to town is
good for everyone.
That's all that really matters.
Isn't that enough?
Might sound fine to the people
who've already closed up shop,
but some of us folks
are still hanging in there!
It's true.
Everyone is
gritting their teeth,
staying open despite
the lack of customers.
But, this is a time
when we should all
be working together
in order to innovate
and stick it out!
Come on, we can do it!
There are so many of us!
All right then,
why don't you let someone
else use your store, huh?
Maybe because we tatami
makers have our pride, okay?
[NUNOBE] Mr. Shiozaki,
is it fair to say that
to those of us still
conducting business?
Let's try to straighten
out this conversation, 'kay?
We'll keep it simple.
What do you think should happen
to the shopping district,
going forward?
The answer is obvious!
The district
should stick around.
I have something
I'd like to say.
It's true that,
thanks to the many efforts
of our very hardworking
Tourism Board.
Manoyama has steadily been
getting more attention lately.
However, it hasn't exactly
led to the revitalization
of the shopping
district, has it?
For that to happen,
the shopping district itself
needs to have some
actual draw of its own.
But despite knowing that,
we still can't seem
to agree on a place
for the pastry shop.
So, that's why I think
we should consider
recommending the school.
What do you all think?
Are you kidding?
Why do that?
So, you're okay
with things as they are?
--That's--
--Calm down, Mr. Iwashita.
How about it, Akiyama?
Will you work with us?
It's for the benefit of the
shopping district, after all.
[IWASHITA]
He's right, Akiyama!
Why on earth would you say no?
You don't live there anymore.
And no one is implying
that you should rent
your shop out for free.
Belem is a reputable
company, Akiyama.
You should consider it.
It could really help us.
Lots of young customers
would come through.
The district really
needs that kick-start.
Please.
Hurry up and make a
decision already, Akiyama!
You have the power to put this
whole issue behind us for good.
Come on!
[TATSUO]
Please consider it, Akiyama!
[MIURA] For the good of
the district and the town!
[NUNOBE]
Please, we need you!
Come out here and party!
It's heaps of fun!
We've got tons of
booze to share with you!
[TAIRA]
Quit hiding in there!
Don't be shy, come on out!
They'll end up
burning me to death
and they don't even know it!
Go away!
[IWASHITA]
Come on, Akiyama!
Just do it, would you?
[NUNOBE] The town really
needs your help right now!
[CHITOSE]
Okay, that's enough.
I believe Akiyama
must have his reasons.
There are lots
of other available,
closed shops besides his.
Yet, the existence
of the shopping district
is in real danger, so...
Maybe we should just accept
that our time here is up.
Stop it!
Don't you give up so easily!
Come on, Queen,
why don't you say something?
I don't know.
You've got to try
to convince these people
that it's for the
town's benefit!
I don't want too, though.
Huh?!
I can't.
This is exactly like
the dragon's story.
None of you are trying
to see it from the other side.
What're you saying?
[YOSHINO] I personally feel
like most of you are right.
And, that you're saying
what you're saying
for the good of the town.
But, for those
who aren't interested,
you're trying
to force it on them.
[USHIMATSU] Is the queen giving
up on revitalizing the town?
No, but this kind
of revitalization
doesn't work for everyone!
Maybe it's idealistic, but...
Listen.
I believe, in order
for this to work,
every one living here must feel
a personal drive for change.
But, if you decide things
by majority rule,
and then, this happens
at the expense
of someone giving something up.
Then, that's not
revitalization at all!
It's just development!
Uh...!
[YOSHINO]
I believe,
nothing like this should be
forced on anyone.
That's not okay.
The answer is for us
to come together,
and save the shopping
district as a team!
I think the queen's
right on this one.
[AKIYAMA]
I'm sorry, everyone.
But please, I beg you
to try to understand.
I don't want to go through
that same awful thing again.
Why? What the hell
happened, Akiyama?
[CHITOSE]
His tenant flew the coop.
Wait, he took off?
You mean the kid that
ran the accessory shop?
How come you never said
anything to anyone about it?
If people found out,
then the Board of Merchants'
contempt for outsiders
would have grown even
stronger than it already was.
To his great credit,
Akiyama didn't
want that to happen.
I was the only one to whom
he told the whole story.
He's been holding
this information in
for a very long time.
When he came around,
looking for a space
to rent eight years ago,
I was anxious to help him
out as much as I could.
He had no ties to Manoyama,
but he said he wanted
to liven things up.
That made me happy.
But, to my surprise,
within less than half a year.
He suddenly up and
disappeared without a trace.
Unfortunately,
I was the guarantor
on his loan from the bank.
This is what came from me
putting my faith in an outsider.
Now I would just like
to be left alone.
All right, then.
I can see that forcing the issue
would be foolish and cruel.
Maybe we should just
forget the whole thing, huh?
How does that sound?
Yes.
[SHIOZAKI]
Um...
[CHITOSE]
Huh?
If you'd like to offer
my place to Belem, you can.
I, of course, had no idea what
happened to Akiyama before.
I thought he mistakenly
assumed the tenant
would make a lot of
money off of his generosity.
And then, meanwhile,
I've been upset about
something silly, like the smell.
I feel ashamed.
I'm sorry.
We have our answer, then.
[SHIOZAKI]
Mm-hm.
Thank you, Mr. Shiozaki!
Mr. Akiyama,
I'd like to apologize for
trying to force this on you,
and I hope you're
willing to forgive us.
Of course I do,
and I'm sorry, too.
Thank you, Queen.
You're an interesting one.
We're lucky to have you.
I've seen you on
TV just like everyone else.
I've heard quite
a few rumors, too.
Do you mind if
I ask you a question?
Okay.
From what I understand,
you don't have any
personal ties to Manoyama.
Why do you work so hard for us?
Well, I guess.
I'm an outsider,
and Manoyama has been
good enough to take me in.
I see.
Thank you, Queen.
Okay, last scene.
In our show,
the dead dragon is going
to suddenly appear
before all of the villagers.
The dragon has learned how
the villagers are feeling,
and she comes to see
them in spirit form.
"Worry not.
I bear you no grudge
for what happened to me.
In truth, you wanted
to join hands with me,
and understand me."
And so, the people stand
before the vision of the dragon.
And with this
newfound understanding,
the young villager girl
offers the dragon's song.
Okay!
♪ Sleep tonight,
go and dream. ♪
♪ Feel the comfort of our song ♪
[USHIMATSU]
Hey, hag.
[CHITOSE]
Hmm?
About the thing with Akiyama.
I had no idea that's
what happened to him.
That's really awful.
So, yeah, I'm sorry.
Huh?
And for what
happened 50 years ago.
Hmm? What was that?
I'm trying to apologize!
Would you let me?
Huh?
Hmph!
I guess it's all water
under the bridge.
[CHITOSE]
Proposed?
How long are you going
to keep skulking around?
Just stop worrying.
The Board of Merchants
will officially participate
in the festival.
Wow, seriously?
Thank you so much!
Your turn, Mr. Kadota.
Uh, yeah, thanks,
I guess we owe you one.
You'd think, by this age,
you'd've learned how
to thank someone properly.
Would you be quiet?
Oh, I know!
On the day of the festival,
why don't you two get up
on stage together?
Maki was just complaining
that they don't have
enough extras yet for the
villagers in the dragon play.
Oh, the play, huh?
Yeah, maybe.
I guess I'd be up for that.
As long as I'm not
playing a zombie.
Nice move, hag!
Okay, Queen!
I'm in!
But I get to play
the village chief!
You don't get to choose
your part, Mr. Kadota!
[USHIMATSU] It's only
natural that's what I'd play!
This is far enough.
Drop me off here.
So, I'll leave it up to you.
The matter we discussed
is in your hands.
[NOGE]
Hey, Queen!
I brought it,
like you asked me to.
[YOSHINO]
Great!
Thank you so much for this.
So, what are you going
to use it for, anyway?
As a prop in the play?
Not quite.
I actually want to use it
as one of the treasures
in the Mizuchi Festival.
Wait, what are
you talking about?
You mean in place
of the golden dragon?
Yeah!
If we make a brand new one
it's going to be
super expensive.
We'll use this guy this year!
But, it's an actual toy.
Hey, this toy is
the Shining Dragon!
Ha! Well, okay, then.
What matters is
how you feel, right?
Thanks, that's right!
That means we now have all
of the Three Sacred Treasures!
Yeah!
Hey, where's Mr. Kadota?
Does anyone know?
Oh. There he is.
Oh, wow.
You're looking a
little down, Mr. Kadota.
What's wrong?
I think we may be facing
the end of Manoyama.
What?
I've been hearing
rumors for a while.
But, plans are apparently
moving forward, now.
We'll be absorbed into Tomikura.
[gasps]
We'll be what?
[SANDAL]
I used to live
on the second floor
of a curry restaurant.
I could eat three naan
just from the smell.
Next time:
"The Eternal Obelisk."