Beef still ain't here?
I don't get it.
Do you think he chickened
out at the last minute?
Everything is clear to me now.
Clear like leftover oden,
left out for three days
and then drained!
[MAKI] Hey, what the
hell are you watching?
Oh, well, I was surfing around
for different clues that
might explain why Mr. Kadota
was drowning in Sakura Pond,
and I just kind
of ended up here.
Why do you ask?
Yeah, I'm not buyin' it.
The Oden Detective!
Have you seen Maki yet?
This looks like
the third episode,
so I'm not in it.
I was a minor character
who made ingredients
for oden in episode two.
[crash]
[SANAE, YOSHINO gasp]
[MAKI]
What the heck was that?
Did something explode?
Wait! It might be dangerous!
Over there!
[YOSHINO]
Mr. Kadota!
Did he escape from the hospital?
Mr. Kadota! Are you okay?
He's burning up!
Sanae, go bring the car around!
Okay!
[USHIMATSU groans]
I'm not... I'm not running away.
I'm not.
Running away?
[MINO]
What? He was in the hospital?
[SHIORI] Yeah, he almost
drowned in Sakura Pond
last night.
And after he was admitted,
he apparently ran out
into the rain
and caught pneumonia.
The whole thing's a mess,
but I think he's gonna be okay.
What the hell was he doing?
Dunno, but I guess that means
I should go ahead and
cancel his plans today.
Huh... What do you
think this is?
Okay, wait a sec,
was he trying to use
his car to drag something
up out of the pond?
[GROUP]
Huh?
[SANAE]
What was it?
Riichan!
You will never believe
what happened last night.
I've seen an incredible photo.
[RIRIKO]
When I got home last night,
my grandma was looking at this.
[YOSHINO]
Is that... Mr. Kadota?
[SANAE]
And Doku?
[RIRIKO]
And that's Grandma.
So those three used to be in a
band together back in the day?
What'd she say about it?
I haven't asked.
I can't ask.
Yeah, where do you even
start asking about this?
Just two old fools
trading ghost stories.
[laughing]
Let's go visit with Doku.
I bet you he'll tell
us all about it.
[DOKU] This sure does
bring back memories.
So you found Chitose
looking at this alone?
Yes.
It's true--
we were in a band together.
Fifty years ago.
Ushimatsu on guitar, I was on
drums, and Chitose played bass.
We called ourselves
"The Garage Band."
[USHIMATSU (SONG)] ♪ All of
your roses are blooming ♪
♪ All of your roses
are blooming ♪
♪ I can see 'em
next door growing ♪
♪ Yeah, they've gotten so red ♪
[USHIMATSU, CHITOSE] ♪ There
ain't nothin' in my garden ♪
♪ only filth where maggots... ♪
Wow, those lyrics are
very creative, aren't they?
Ushimatsu gets that credit.
No surprise there.
[DOKU]
Chitose wrote the music.
A boy and girl singing together
was pretty rare at that time.
[CHITOSE (SONG)] ♪ So fair is
foul, foul is fair ♪
♪ Is that what I'm
supposed to believe ♪
♪ You think the words that... ♪
Grandma's really singing.
She's got a nice voice.
This was the Garage Band's
very biggest number:
"Those Roses are Blooming."
Good times.
But screaming like this in
Manoyama fifty years ago
didn't turn too
many heads our way.
[DOKU]
We were young.
We thought if we went to Tokyo,
it'd work out somehow.
It was all Chitose's idea.
She said that since I was
heading off to college in Tokyo,
we should all go and
keep our band together.
But she was the only daughter
of a confectionary owner.
And Ushimatsu would
inherit his dad's farm.
Their parents were
never gonna let them go.
We were ready to
run away from home,
to leave Manoyama for Tokyo,
and never return.
We planned to go through with
it on the night of a festival.
We'd leave by train while
everyone was distracted,
and then it would be
"So long, Manoyama!"
Beef still ain't here.
I don't get it.
Do you think he chickened
out at the last minute?
[DOKU]
We waited for him,
but in the end,
Ushimatsu never showed.
Why didn't he?
You'd have to ask him.
But while we were
waiting on the platform,
Ushimatsu was off
someplace else.
[USHIMATSU yelling]
[ONLOOKER 16A]
What is he doing?
[ONLOOKER 16B]
That's Kadota's bonehead son!
♪ All of your roses
are blooming ♪
[FESTIVAL WORKER 16B]
You're going to curse us!
[FESTIVAL WORKER 16C]
Pull him down from there!
Get down, damn it!
Come on, kid, shut up!
[FESTIVAL WORKER 16C] Hey,
you're giving us bad luck!
[FESTIVAL WORKERS yelling]
Bastards! Let go!
[DOKU] This is a picture that
somebody took that day.
He looks totally
out of control.
[SHIORI] Well, that sure hasn't
changed much for him, has it?
It was because of that
incident that the festival
was never to be held again.
I went to Tokyo alone,
so the band officially broke up.
Ushimatsu and Chitose have
been at odds ever since.
Yeah, this actually
explains a lot.
If you're the reason
a festival cancels,
you're practically
a war criminal!
I'm surprised he was able
to keep living here after that.
It wasn't as bad as you think.
It's not like that festival
was all that popular.
People probably thought
its time had come, anyway.
What happened to
the float and the guitar?
They never pulled it up;
they just left it in there.
I would have thought
after fifty years,
it would've all
have fallen apart.
So we think
Mr. Kadota noticed something
and tried to pull it up?
He was probably trying to
get rid of whatever it was
so he wouldn't have to live
through the embarrassment again.
[YOSHINO]
I wonder what made Mr. Kadota
try to perform on top of
the shrine float, anyway.
[SANAE] He was probably
afraid of going to Tokyo.
And then he just
went a little crazy.
I never would've
thought our cranky boss
was the type to try and leave
home when he was young.
I'm more surprised
by your granny!
Hidden depths of coolness.
[KINU]
Chitose!
We can't seem to stop
causing you problems, can we?
I'm really sorry about that.
Yes, I guess that's true.
But you know,
I believe Ushimatsu
still feels guilty
about what happened
between the two of you
fifty years ago.
I've wondered,
what on earth could ever
have made you want
to marry that guy?
Well, what on earth
could've possibly
made you want to be
in a band with him?
In the beginning,
I was fully convinced
that he was tough as nails,
a real rocker.
Well, if the truth
be known, he still is.
Would you like some manju?
Thank you, yes.
[SANDAL] The Cryptid Twelve's
Encyclopedia of UMA.
May I present file number one:
The Mothman.
It's slow on its feet,
but flies at a land speed
of 160 kilometers an hour.
Okay, show us how you fly!
It is only pretend!
[CROWD laughing]
Hola, Ririko!
Hola!
This looks like fun!
Seems like more
people around than usual.
[SANAE] I think people heard
the Mr. Kadota rumors
and came to watch the drying.
They wanna check
out what's down there.
[SHIORI]
I still can't see anything.
[SANAE] The part that was
sticking out of the surface
yesterday broke off
when Mr. Kadota
tried to pull it away.
I bet we'll be able
to get a good look
once the water level
goes down more.
I'm kind of looking
forward to it now!
I wonder what
that festival was like.
Fifty years sure is a long time.
[CHITOSE, USHIMATSU] ♪ Well you
can keep all your roses foul, ♪
♪ I don't want
your maggots fair ♪
♪ Why's my garden
not bloomin' ♪
♪  When will spring come
give me my own roses fair ♪
[faint clapping]
Well, that's about
what I'd expect
from the downtown
summer festival.
Don't you think?
It's not frustrating
for you, Poison?
It feels like the world
is going through
all these massive changes.
And yet, here we are,
trapped in this little town
with no visible way out.
How are you all okay with this?
You're stuck in your
stupid old ways!
How can you just sit around,
laughing like idiots?
What the hell are you doing?
Don't you wanna do something
interesting for once?
You're livin' tiny lives
in the middle of nowhere!
All just waitin' around to die!
[CHITOSE laughs]
What? What're you laughing at?
You're getting a little
heated, there, Beef.
Yeah, of course I am.
It's summer, right?
[CHITOSE]
Tokyo.
Tokyo?
[CHITOSE]
Right!
Poison said he's taking an
exam for a college there.
And if he passes,
I think we should go with him!
[USHIMATSU]
You mean to college?
Oh, hell no!
Not for college, for the band!
We'll go to Tokyo
and give everyone chills
with our totally original sound!
Huh?
But what about your family?
Oh, I'm not going to tell them.
They'd only try to stop me.
But it's going to be okay.
I don't care if they disown me.
Besides, even if they do,
I know you'll stick
with me, won't you?
Uh... Yeah.
Hey, there you are, son!
Look, this year's kabura
turned out pretty great!
C'mere! Have one!
What do you think?
They're pretty tasty, huh?
[USHIMATSU]
Sure.
I guess all this
farm can hope for
is that they'll turn out this
good next year, too. Right?
What's wrong?
Nothing, Dad.
[YAMADA] Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, that sounds great.
I'll go ahead and fax
over the application
for the food stall now,
so fill out all the
required lines for me,
then send it back in
as soon as you can.
It's early and we've
already had so many calls!
I know, right?
So many people are
showing up for the drying!
It kinda makes me wish
we could have planned
an event for it
from the beginning.
I think we should do
something at the palace!
Agreed!
We're working on an
expansion of the market.
They're at it
right now, actually!
Sanae and Maki.
Oh, here's the application!
What about the queen?
She's doing some
research right now
with the UMA Minister.
Maybe this is it.
Mizuchi Festival.
[RIRIKO] The Mizuchi
is actually a water god.
It also means water orochi.
Orochi. Like a dragon?
Wait a second.
You mean like the dragon
in the Manoyama folktale?
A long time before
they made Sakura Pond,
there was a small pond
and a shrine.
And that's where Manoyama's
dragon was enshrined.
[YOSHINO] The origin of the
Mizuchi Festival is not certain,
but after Sakura Pond was built,
and the shrine had to be moved,
the festival was changed
to be conducted
on the water's surface,
which became tradition.
They loaded up the shrine on
a float and crossed the pond!
So that's where
Mr. Kadota climbed up.
[SANAE] That festival had
been held for a long time,
then, huh?
Sakura Pond was created
around 100 years ago,
which means it continued
for about another fifty years
until Mr. Kadota
did what he did.
This is my stepmom's.
It's an album from back then.
It even has some nice
pictures of the festival.
Good photographer,
her ex father-in-law.
So your stepmom's
previous father-in-law?
It's better not to ask.
It's a festival, but
hardly anyone's there.
I guess that explains
why nobody got upset
when it was cancelled.
Doku did say that it wasn't very
popular among the residents.
[USHIMATSU'S DAD]
Ushimatsu!
Hey aren't you going
to the festival?
I dunno, maybe.
What about you, Dad?
[USHIMATSU'S DAD]
No, not this year.
I'll just leave it to
you young folks.
Back ain't what it used to be!
[laughs]
[USHIMATSU]
Is this the only way?
Do you have to go to Tokyo?
Is Manoyama really no good?
[TV music]
[SHOP OWNER 16A] Sorry,
we're closing up for the day.
[USHIMATSU]
What am I--
Dammit!
[USHIMATSU]
I'm not running away!
I refuse to run away!
I'll fight!
I won't run!
I won't!
I'm not gonna run off to Tokyo.
I'm staying here!
I'm gonna wake them all up!
Wake up those fools!
Wake up this whole damn town!
[yelling]
[gasps]
Mr. Kadota!
Thank goodness!
It's great to see you waking up!
Oh. Yeah.
Good news. Mr. Kadota's awake.
Oh, really?
I was kinda hoping
he'd kick the bucket.
That's too bad.
Doku told us what
happened fifty years ago.
Your singing was
very cool, Grandma.
I think I vaguely
remember that.
He also told us you thought
about leaving Manoyama.
That's all in the past
and it's forgotten.
Ririko.
I want you to listen to me.
Whatever you might
be thinking right now,
whatever dreams you
might have for yourself,
when you get old,
you forget about them.
You stop caring
one way or the other.
That's why, granddaughter.
Before that happens to you,
you should get out there,
and you should do
whatever you want to do.
I wonder what that little
thing over there could be?
I never thought I'd see the day
when they drained the pond!
So that's the
famous shrine float.
It's not surprising that
it's lost its original shape.
You'd never know what it
was unless someone told you.
I wonder if that
thing is a guitar.
[MAKI]
What thing?
[SANAE]
I can't tell at all.
[YOSHINO]
This is nice, huh?
Nobody announced it or anything,
but people just kind
of showed up!
And they're all having fun!
I'm sure the pond has seen
some interesting things!
[GIRL 16B]
Should we help it?
[speaking Spanish]
A place where people gather.
A place everyone returns to.
You know what I'm thinking?
It must have been a
day not unlike this one
when someone first suggested
they hold a festival.
Hey, guys, what would you think
about possibly
reviving the festival?
I'd love that!
[GROUP chattering]
Now that they're leaving,
it's actually kind of hard
to say goodbye.
Yeah, they're headed to
Kushiro in Hokkaido after this.
For Kussie in Lake Kussharo?
How do I tell her,
"When you're back,
the B&amp;B in my heart
will be waiting!"
You should simplify and say,
"One night, love, please!"
--Claro.
--[KANEDA] Hey, Constanza!
Give me one night. Please, love!
You mind your manners.
[speaking Spanish]
Hasta luego.
[LUCIA speaking Spanish]
[USHIMATSU]
So Queen, tell me.
[YOSHINO]
Hm?
They found some stuff
at the bottom of the pond,
didn't they?
Yeah, there was a bunch
of things down there,
but the maintenance workers
were sure to take it all away.
Oh, I see.
[YOSHINO] Anyway, I've got
something to ask you.
[USHIMATSU]
Hm?
[YOSHINO] Would you like
to revive the festival?
The Mizuchi Festival
from fifty years ago?
We could bring it back!
Nobody in town wants that.
It would be a
huge waste of time.
I don't think that's true!
You should've seen
them at the drying!
Everyone was having
a great time!
It felt like a festival!
It was so lovely.
And I think it'd be really
nice if they had a place
to gather like that
here in Manoyama!
And, perhaps most importantly
I heard you.
[USHIMATSU]
Huh?
[YOSHINO]
You were talking in your sleep.
"I'm gonna wake them up.
Wake up this whole damn town!"
Do whatever you want.
Revive the Mizuchi festival?
That's crazy!
We'd have to find backers
and start setting up meetings.
We'd need help from every
single person in Manoyama!
That's right,
and we'll convince them!
The budget's a big problem, too.
We have to build a
new shrine float for a start,
and that's just the beginning.
We'll need lots of other things.
What other things?
You know. Other things.
[GROUP]
Hm?
The Three Sacred Treasures.
What, Mr. Shigaraki?
What Three Sacred Treasures?
The Staff, the Hanging Drum,
and the Golden Dragon.
These items have
been passed down
for generations of
the Mizuchi Festival.
If you can't gather
them together,
then you cannot
revive the festival.
The problem, I'm afraid,
is their whereabouts
have been a mystery
for quite some time.
Well, then, okay!
This sounds like our challenge!
We'll find those missing
treasures, I swear!
[SANDAL] That was the first
time Mr. Shigaraki ever spoke,
so I was pretty surprised.
We went to karaoke after that.
It was fun.
Next time:
"The Sphinx's Antics."