♪
[CHILDREN chatter]
[RIRIKO]
Ever since I was little,
people have told me
that I'm a strange girl.
Wanna play?
Okay!
Wow!
Pretty, huh?
[RIRIKO] For some reason,
I could never laugh with them.
This is delicious!
Oh, hey, look! It says
I have great luck!
Yeah, I'm not really
loving mine.
What's "a little lucky"?
Bring me another one, please.
Hey, what's with all those tiny
little sips over there, huh?
You gotta chug that thing, girl!
You gotta chug it!
Regretfully, as Queen, I think
I should keep my wits about me
in public and also keep
an eye on you guys.
Are you kidding me?
What a bummer!
Shiori, who does that?
Orange juice with your shiokara?
Well, I'm the designated driver.
And it's actually
not bad at all!
[RIRIKO]
Urchin.
Soy sauce on pudding, right?
When I was little we used
to put honey on cucumbers
and say it tasted like melon!
You can also put yogurt on
shiokara to make caviar.
Seriously? Let's try it!
Angelica, do you have
any yogurt back there?
I have to go home, guys.
What? Already?
Thanks, Shi- chan . You didn't
have to leave with me.
Oh, no, it's okay.
My grandpa worries, anyway.
So, tell me. Did you actually
want to stay and hang out?
I don't care.
[SHIORI chuckles] You know,
you've really changed lately,
since meeting Yoshi and
the girls. You're more cheerful.
[RIRIKO gasps]
I wonder. Is that really true?
A Rural Romance in Manoyama.
[USHIMATSU] It's sort of a
matchmaking tour and it's been
organized by the singles in
the Community Club, locally.
Hey, Yamada! You're in that
singles' group, right?
Yeah. I mean, I have
a girlfriend, though.
You held out on me?
Who is this girl?
If she's hot,
I'm gonna kill you.
[YAMADA] What are you even
talking about? You're married!
Anyway, it appears that
there are only three females
who have signed up for this
dang matchmaking tour thing.
Kindaichi's the leader
of the singles' group,
and came in here
crying about it.
[KANEDA] Even if we're
only talking about three,
we can't let them get away.
How do we convince three city
girls to marry and settle
here in Manoyama?
So, he's pretty serious, then.
[USHIMATSU] He is, and that's
where you come in, Queen.
I don't care if there
are only three of them.
I need you to figure out a
way to grab hold of these
city girls' hearts and
not let them get away!
[YOSHINO] So, what we need
to do is re-vamp the plan.
We need to come up with
the perfect itinerary
for this three-day,
two-night tour.
Does anyone else here think that
we should start by re-naming it?
totally agree with you
except for one thing:
they've already been using
this name to advertise.
Now, let's see. How 'bout
we go through the
Community Club's
suggestions for activities.
A karaoke duet tournament on
a rented, decked out party bus.
A thrilling afternoon
of fortune-telling
with lunch at Angelica's.
Who will be connected by the
lovers' fated red somen?
Show off your excellent
cooking skills.
Compete in this
cooking challenge
using local vegetables!
The way to every prince's heart
is through his stomach?
Come and play the Chupa Game.
One person is the Chupa,
and you must obey their orders.
But if the Chupa issues orders
to the Hero, watch out?
Were they seriously
going to do this stuff?
[YOSHINO]
Hm...
What kind of activities
would you want to do?
Um. Well, the obvious thing
would be to go to all the
tasty shops in town, right?
I think it's probably best
to avoid this area, though.
No, we've gotta be
honest and show them
this place as it really is.
We have to help them
fall completely in love
with every part of Manoyama!
How about if they stayed
in an old-style house?
I think that can
be pretty charming.
And I know no one's
taken my old place yet.
That's such a great idea!
We should give them experiences
they can't get anywhere else!
Exactly! Something creative
and filled with the discoveries
and surprises you can
only get in the country!
Hey, Rii- chan ,
you're the creative one.
Do you have any brilliant ideas?
A Get-Your-Blood-Sucked-
By-A-Leech tour?
[YOSHINO, SHIORI gasp]
Okay, that might be a
little bit too creative.
What'd be the point of
having their blood sucked?
A leech sucking out bad
blood is detoxifying.
They use them in Ayurveda,
a type of traditional
Indian medicine.
You mean like
those doctor fish?
I do think you're headed
in the right direction,
but we might need to think
sparkly-shiny for these girls.
Hey, this brewery's sake'
is pretty tasty stuff.
What if we brought them here?
Sake' really is
booming right now,
so a tasting-tour might be good!
Oh! See that mountain?
There's a river on it
with so many fireflies,
it's almost scary!
I bet most city girls
would freak out over it!
Oh, I would! A night
full of fireflies?
I thought bugs were
always out, for you.
Well, yeah, they are,
but fireflies don't count.
Did you have a lot of fireflies
where you came from, Yoshino?
Definitely. I grew up
in a harbor town.
Oh, cool! We should
go see them together!
Like, scout it out for work,
and have a firefly sleepover!
That sounds great! I love it!
And you know, the bed next
to mine is always available!
[SHIORI giggles] Aw!
Wait, what? I don't get it!
Huh. Sake-tasting, fireflies,
and a night in an
old-style house.
Hm! Not bad at all, ladies.
Thank you, but I can't help
thinking it's missing something.
How about if they
got to spend a day
as the head of the
Tourism Board?
They can wear the Chupakabura
costume as much as they want!
[SANAE]
What are we trying to do?
Show them a good time,
or punish them?
[SHIORI]
You're right, though, Yoshi.
We need one more
thing on the agenda
that really sells
them on the town.
How about teaching them
the Manoyama Dance?
What Manoyama Dance?
Oh, it's lovely,
and it's been passed down
here for generations.
All the girls who grow up in
town are taught that dance
in school when
they're very young.
I remember that! I loved
learning it as a kid.
Yep, I had to learn it back
when I was little, too.
Is it really still a thing?
This is so perfect! Exposure to
a local traditional art!
We could give lessons
to the girls on the tour,
then we can all dance
together at the end!
Not me. I can't dance.
Oh, don't worry
about that, Rii- chan !
I'm a terrible dancer, too!
If we all practice together,
I'm sure we'll get it.
Keep in mind, this dance has a
very long history in this town.
Try to take it seriously.
You just leave it to me!
As queen, it's my duty to
learn it inside and out and
make the town proud!
I can be your dance teacher
if you'd like me to, Yoshino!
[YOSHINO gasps]
Alright, my own tutor!
I don't... think I'll be able
to dance like the Queen.
[YOSHINO, SHIORI gasp]
Oh, jeez, come on.
You've always kind of avoided
this stuff, huh, Rii- chan ?
You don't have to dance with us.
We've probably got
it covered, no worries!
[bell rings]
[RIRIKO]
It's time for me to head home.
Okay! Why don't I
give you a ride?
Thanks, but the buses
are still running.
Would you accept the invitation
if I offered you a ride?
[RIRIKO]
I...
It's no problem at all,
and I'd like to, Rii- chan .
Good night, then!
See you tomorrow!
Say hi to old granny.
[KINU]
So, I'm curious.
Why don't you want to
do the Manoyama Dance
with the other girls?
Mainly because I don't
like being told I have to
do something just because
of some tradition.
[KINU giggles] You sound
just like my husband.
[RIRIKO]
Uh?
Sorry, I shouldn't
have said that.
I imagine it doesn't make
you happy to hear it.
But, you see, I mean
it as a compliment.
I like that you aren't
afraid to be an individual.
[KINU]
Okay, hop on in.
Good night. I'm heading out now.
[CHITOSE]
Alright, good night.
[RIRIKO]
I'm home.
Well, hello there.
I'm guessing Shi must have
given you a ride home?
So you're helping out
with the Community Club's
matchmaking tour. I feel sorry
for them because there's
no way that's going to go well.
[RIRIKO] Grandma, do you
think I've changed?
[CHITOSE]
Hm?
Why, has something
happened with you?
You're still Ririko.
And you're perfect
just the way you are.
[YOSHINO]
What do you think?
Did I maybe say something
I shouldn't have?
No, and as long as you don't try
to force her to dance with us,
I think it'll be fine.
You and Rii- chan
have been pretty close
since you were
little girls, right?
[SHIORI]
Mm-hm!
We've been friends since we
started elementary school.
I wonder if Chitose
got angry with her
when she didn't end up
learning the Manoyama Dance.
She seems like she'd be
strict about that stuff.
I know it's hard to believe,
but granny Chitose is
pretty soft on Rii- chan .
[YOSHINO]
Is she really?
If she wasn't, she probably
wouldn't allow Rii- chan
to do half the things
she does with us.
It's a bunny, you see?
It's cute!
[SHIORI gasps]
What is that? A shrimp?
[RIRIKO]
Anomalocaris.
Anomama... no...
Is it something
you can eat?
No, not anymore.
They've been extinct for
a very long time now.
Oh, wow! You're like an
animal expert, Rii- chan !
[gasps] Is it okay to
call you Rii- chan ?
[RIRIKO]
Huh?
[TEACHER]
Cheese! Smile for me, Ririko!
[RIRIKO groans]
[BOTH gasp]
[WOMEN gasp]
[YOSHINO] Are you here for the
Rural Romance Manoyama Tour?
That's right!
[YOSHINO]
Kiyomi Hiragi.
[KIYOMI chuckles]
[YOSHINO]
Ayana Nakatsugawa.
And Izumi Koyama, right?
Uh-huh!
Welcome to Manoyama!
My name is Yoshino Koharu,
Queen of Chupakabura.
I'll be your tour guide!
And I'm her assistant,
Maki Midorikawa.
[ALL]
It's very nice to meet you!
[IZUMI] I was wondering,
is it just the three of us?
Are we all that signed up?
[YOSHINO]
Uh, yeah!
We would've had to cancel it,
if any of you hadn't shown!
[AYANA]
Uh... what?
[YOSHINO] Uh, however! If you
focus on the positive side,
it's like a reverse-harem!
And you get your pick
of all the men in town!
He's not too bad, right?
Eh. Too old for my taste.
[TAKAMIZAWA] Alright, alright,
ladies, I'm your driver today.
However, if you princesses
need anything else, well...
[ALL gasp]
How gross! That didn't
actually work on you two!
Takamizawa, you're a
married man! So, back off, sir!
I should've known that he
would already have a wife.
Don't worry!
There are heaps of handsome
men from the Community Club
just waiting for your arrival!
Well, we can't guarantee
that "handsome" part, though.
Okay, now seems like a good
time to go over the itinerary.
First, you have a welcome lunch!
Ippei Taira.
You can read my name
backwards and forwards
and it's still the same name.
I'm 39. Work in non-profit.
Hey, wait a minute,
I thought you were 42?
So, this year's actually your
bad-luck year, isn't that right?
No, didn't you know?
In Manoyama,
they believe a man's
bad luck year is 39!
[WOMEN giggle]
I'm Kakimura.
I grow Kabura and rice,
and I'm a young 33 years old!
Hey, I'm Shibukawa.
I'm a former sushi chef.
Former?
I'm in training now to
be a competitive eater!
Uh, so... the thing is.
The majority of the
Community Club members
are at work during the day.
So, for right now, we're going
to begin with the ones
who could make it to lunch.
--[door clatters]
--[bell rings]
Hey, sorry I'm so late!
Hello, dear brother. What on
earth brings you here today?
Matchmaking! I'm a member
of the club. That okay?
Are you crazy?
You're still in high school.
But I'm graduating next year.
Wait, shouldn't you be in class?
No, not today! It's a holiday.
Oh, he's still in
high school! What a cutie!
Pretty sure that's
against the law.
[IZUMI]
Huh?
[ERIKA sighs]
You old desperate hags.
Uh. Pardon me. What was that?
Sorry for the wait!
I welcome you.
Today's lunch is a
special dish, which I call
"The Fated Red Threads" somen!
Put your faith in the old legend
and look to find who your
fated red somen leads to.
You decided to go
with that, huh?
♪
So handsome!
And Scandanavian!
Subtle song choice.
[YOSHINO]
Okay!
I certainly hope you all
enjoyed your somen for lunch!
Next up, we'll take a trip
around downtown Manoyama,
and then visit the shopping
arcade where some members
of the Community Club work.
May I ask why Sandal is
coming along with us?
Yeah, is he trying
to swoop in? Damn!
Just calm down.
We need to make
Manoyama more appealing,
even if it means
getting his help.
I mean, he can't steal them all.
We'll just take
whoever's left over!
Do you have absolutely
no sense of pride, man?
Is he a member of the
Community Club, too?
No, I'm fairly positive
that he's not.
Hey, Sandal, what're you--?
You do realize this is a
matchmaking tour, right?
Match Three master, here!
Yeah, that's not exactly the
kind of match we're going for.
Know what I'm best at?
Killing blue pieces.
I hardly recognize the place.
There are ten times as many
people here as
there usually are.
[KANEDA] The single guys
in the Community Club
from the next town over heard
rumors and came to check it out.
Like a herd of beasts.
[SHIORI] If only it was always
this lively around here, huh?
[SANAE] Oh, Noge! The women are
coming, so you should move those
magazines as far
back as possible.
Do we really need
to be that careful?
Now that I think about it,
the Queen and you ministers
are women, too, you know!
Why don't you drop the
tour stuff and marry a man
from Manoyama?
I'm still very focused
on my career.
Don't think of it that way,
as a choice between
career and marriage.
[NOGE]
It's true.
There's nothing wrong with
a stay-at-home husband.
Oh, you're one of those guys
who would jump at the chance,
aren't you?
[SANAE sighs]
[KANEDA gasps]
Here they are!
[NOGE, KANEDA gasp]
They're cute.
I'm Kindaichi, and I'm the
head of the singles group!
It's a pleasure to
meet you ladies!
Oh. What's this?
[KIYOMI gasps]
Oh, it's red somen.
It's what we had for lunch.
It's like we're bound by this
red thread like the legend says.
You gotta be kidding me. That
somen thing actually worked?
It's not very romantic,
though, or is it?
[KANEDA] When you need
directions, I'm your man!
If there's one thing I know,
it's the local streets! Ha, ha.
[KIYOMI]
Thanks!
[CHITOSE grunts]
[door clatters]
Huh?
What, did something happen?
[RIRIKO]
No, nothing.
Have you eaten at
all yet, today?
[RIRIKO]
Yes.
Oh, is that true?
[CHITOSE]
Sheesh!
Why do they feel the need to
ship 'em in like this, anyway?
Are you finished for the day?
Next is a barbeque
at Sakura Pond.
After that, we'll introduce them
to the Manoyama Dance.
Are you dancing, too?
No, I'm not.
Okay, then. Why don't you
just come home early?
[RIRIKO grunts]
Were the three of you
already friends before this?
Yeah, we're coworkers.
Poor Kiyomi. She just had
her heart broken, didn't you?
Hey, come on, Izumi.
That's really not cool.
Don't worry, I'll make
you forget all about it!
What, are you trying
to get a head start
or something, Kindaichi?
I can't believe people still
use come-on lines like that.
It's so cheesy!
Yeah, they don't even
use those on TV anymore.
That makes it
kinda novel, though!
Yeah, it does.
[TAIRA gasps]
You mean that
stuff's okay again?
Well, in that case, I can
make her forget, too!
Don't you think you should
maybe get a real job first?
Oh, good! Looks like
they're having fun!xc
I have to admit,
I was worried at first.
But you didn't even
know what the tour was!
I'm searching, you see.
Uh?
I'm searching for a place.
Where lovers have shared
their romantic moments.
A memory from the
ever-so-distant past.
Memory of...?
I want to find proof.
Of how the two of them lived.
[SHIORI]
Yoshi! Time to get started!
Hurry up, come on!
'Kay! I'll See you later,
Rii- chan . You good?
[RIRIKO]
Mm-hm.
♪
Oh! The Manoyama Dance.
It's a local dance, passed down
for many generations.
[KIYOMI]
Uh-huh.
I don't know if
they've told you,
but long ago, a fearsome
dragon lived in Manoyama.
Hey, what're you trying to do?
Don't scare her, Kadota!
Who says I'm trying
to scare her?
I'm informing her of
an important lesson
in Manoyama's history.
I'm pretty sure there's
a stone dragon idol
enshrined around
here someplace.
[KIYOMI]
Really? A dragon?
[USHIMATSU]
That's right.
A dragon came here
from far away,
and, taking the form
of a young woman,
it made its nest in the pond.
However, the dragon
hates revelry.
That's why, when we dance
cheerfully and play music,
the beast is kept at bay.
So, the Manoyama Dance was
created in order to keep
the dragon away from the town
for generations to come.
[ALL giggle]
[USHIMATSU]
Hm?
[YOSHINO] Mr. Kadota!
Have you seen Rii- chan ?
No, she seemed like
she wasn't feeling well,
so maybe she left.
I wonder if she's okay.
I'll try texting her
a little later.
What?
[MAKI, SANAE yelp]
[MEN groan]
[ALL shout]
I thought there wasn't rain
in the weather forecast!
Yeah, I know!
I'm pretty sure it said there
was only a ten percent chance.
[NOGE sighs]
So, fun fact.
The dragon that lives here
is actually a water god.
You idiot! Are you trying
to make them anxious?
Is this it? Is this the
stone idol Mr. Kadota
was talking about before?
It looks like it hasn't been
taken care of in a long time.
[ALL yelp]
[ALL gasp]
That's not good, you guys.
♪
[SANDAL] The matchmaking tour
really pissed off that dragon.
I'm talking totally,
super-duper pissed.
Next time:
"The Forgotten Requiem."