[YOSHINO]
I'm back!
[TAKAMIZAWA] Huh! Looks like
the queen has returned!
Did you have a
relaxing trip home?
Yeah! I really did!
[phone rings]
[YOSHINO]
Hey, Maki!
I just got to the station.
Where are you?
[MAKI] We're close to
the station, actually.
Are you already on the bus?
We're gonna get back
sooner than we thought,
so we could come pick you up.
[YOSHINO] Oh, awesome!
I would love that!
The bus hasn't left yet,
so I'm sure it's fine.
Uh, please excuse me,
Takamizawa!
[YOSHINO]
So, how was Tokyo?
[SANAE]
Oh, same as always, I guess.
I still can't believe how few
traffic lights there are here.
[MAKI]
How about you?
I don't even need to ask.
It's true,
she looks so cheerful.
Huh? What do you mean?
Ask me!
We can all chat about it later.
[SANAE]
Why are the lights on?
[YOSHINO] Uh...
Maybe Shiori and Riichan?
[SANAE] The Tourism Board
Office was closed, though.
[GROUP chattering]
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[GROUP chattering]
What the--?
Look, Yoshi and the
girls are back! Hola!
[GROUP]
Hola!
[GROUP speaking Spanish]
[MAKI]
Safe birth?
Hey, no worries, you guys!
Hola just means
hello in Spanish.
Our new friends are from Spain!
Wait, from Spain?
[SHIORI] I didn't know what
to make of them either at first,
but I promise
they're not scary!
They wanted to show
they weren't dangerous,
so they had these t-shirts
made for their trip,
but they apparently mixed up
the word for "safe"
with "safe birth,"
which is a little awkward.
[SANAE]
Oh, okay.
They tried to write
"safe" in kanji,
but they made a typo and it
converted to "safe birth."
That's an easy mistake to make.
These are the members
of the Cryptid Twelve.
What's a "cryptid"?
[RIRIKO] Cryptid is another word
for unidentified life form.
Our visitors investigate
and research
unidentified life forms
around the world.
They call themselves
"the twelve chosen ones."
And they learned
about it from this.
[USHIMATSU] They came
all the way here to see
the Chupakabura in Manoyama.
The only one ever seen in Japan!
Which only proves
that our dear old town
is now famous throughout
the entire world!
[laughing]
Seeing as they came
for the Chupakabura,
I was thrilled to welcome 'em.
So, I decided to
open up the palace
and throw them a
big party to celebrate!
[laughing]
[SHIBUKAWA]
This is called sushi!
O, sí!
Sushi es muy delicioso!
[KAKIMURA]
What do you like best?
Maguro, toro, ika,
shrimp, tamagoyaki?
Ah! Me gusta sukiyaki!
No, no.
Sukiyaki is not sushi!
The guys in the singles
group seem totally thrilled.
I bet they're excited
to meet some new
international
marriage prospects!
[YOSHINO sighs]
So tired.
How did your vacation
with your family go?
I'm really glad I went back.
I ended up getting to see
a bunch of old friends
while I was there,
and go to the festival!
Oh, what's your festival like?
There's a shrine
float that's shaped
like a big boat and they
carry it around town.
It's not that big of a festival,
but we get a good
number of people
from neighboring towns,
so it's still pretty lively!
Everyone there
is super friendly.
It's kind of lovely, really.
You know, I don't think I've
ever heard you get so excited
about anything to do
with your hometown before.
[laughs]
I've always thought
I didn't like the country,
but I think it's
actually grown on me.
It's a place I can
always return to.
[SHIORI]
A place to return to.
[gasps] Except...
[YOSHINO]
Except what?
I was just thinking how
when your term as Queen ends,
chances are, you'll probably
head back home.
[SANAE]
What's with you guys?
Did someone die?
[MAKI]
I brought everyone some snacks!
Let's try 'em!
Oh, yummy!
I'll go make some tea!
Ah, I almost forgot,
I brought back some
gifts for you, too!
Yep, so did I!
[SANAE, MAKI]
Here! Ahh!
We bought the same thing!
[YOSHINO] I guess we're
all pretty tired.
Do you want me to drive
you home, Riichan?
I said I'd be
home late tonight.
[YOSHINO]
Cool! Another drink, then?
Place to return.
[RIRIKO]
What you said earlier.
The thing is...
I moved in with my
grandma when I was little,
and haven't left Manoyama since.
So I guess I didn't
know exactly
what you meant by that.
So you're saying
you've never felt
like leaving Manoyama before?
I've honestly never
thought about it.
If I were ever to leave,
then my grandma
would be all alone here.
She would be fine on her own
for one night, though.
So! Why don't you stay
here tonight?
You're right.
I'll text her and let her know.
[YOSHINO] Okay! We're back
together, and ready to work!
So let's start by tackling
a new problem!
That being said, I have
no clue what that might be,
and therefore
have no plan at all.
[laughs]
Well, while you guys
were on vacation,
Mr. Kadota had us
do some research
on the guest lodging
problem in Manoyama.
They've recently sorted out
the laws for B&amp;Bs,
so he wondered if
we could find a way
to make use of all the
empty houses in town.
[MAKI] The Cryptid Twelve
guys showing up is
a good example of why we should!
They're a perfect chance
to create a model case!
But we do need to be aware
of the potential issues
that come with B&amp;Bs.
What do you mean, issues?
Accommodating foreign
tourists can be sensitive.
Unlike hotels in big cities
and tourist destinations,
B&amp;Bs require direct
cooperation from the locals
in the area.
So there are always
potential issues
regarding basic
cultural differences.
Like with our new
friends here, for instance.
People felt a bit
uneasy about them
until they knew
exactly what the visitors
had come here to do.
It's true. Riichan and I
were a little freaked out
the first time they
surrounded us!
You know what I find funny
about this case, though?
Knowing what they're here for
only makes them more bizarre.
[MAKI]
And then there's the obvious
language barrier problem.
Hang on. Where's Riichan?
[CRYPTIDS speaking Spanish]
[RIRIKO] The Mothman.
Mokele-mbembe.
Matsudodon.
[SERGENO]
Matsudodon!
[CRYPTIDS speaking Spanish]
Looks like they're overcoming
the language barrier!
Behold the power of
the international language
of UMA!
I mean, there are
also some pretty good
translation apps out there.
So, maybe we should believe
in the Manoyamans a little more.
I'm just curious what
the Cryptids are actually doing
here every day.
Well, they're
gathering information
about Chupakabura sightings,
they're exploring the mountains,
and they're taking pictures
of old source material.
What else, partying?
[USHIMATSU growls]
[chuckles]
Comprehendo?
Chupakabura mask!
Guau! Como mola!
Esta sukiyaki!
Muy better than sushi.
[SHIBUKAWA] No, no,
sushi is numero uno!
It's the muy best!
[GROUP chattering]
I guess this is where
they're meeting tonight.
You wanna go?
No way!
We came all the way here.
I say we should eat!
'Kay, real talk,
anyone have a clue
how long the Cryptids
plan to stay here?
Until they find the Chupakabura.
If that's true, they'll
never get to go home.
[ANGELICA] I heard they
plan to stay until the drying.
[YOSHINO]
What's that?
Sandal was just telling
them about the drying
and they seemed
really interested.
They said they didn't want
to leave until they'd seen it.
[SANAE]
So, what is this "drying"?
[TAIRA] I would've thought that
the Tourism Board was involved.
The water's drained
from Sakura Pond.
[YOSHINO]
All of it?
I guess you didn't know
it's actually a reservoir.
So, if you open the gates...
That's right. They stopped
using it for irrigation
a long time ago, so it hasn't
been dried like that
for several decades now.
Maybe for not for about
seventy years, I'd guess?
Not for seventy years?
[NOGE] The number of black
bass have been increasing,
and that damages the ecosystem,
so this is a common way
of addressing that.
It's supposed to happen
tomorrow, isn't it?
The opening of
the gates, I mean.
And once they've been opened,
it should take about
two weeks to dry
depending on the weather.
[USHIMATSU] Hey, hey, hey,
what's everyone talking about?
[NOGE] We've just been
discussing the drying tomorrow.
Huh? Ah, yes, the drying!
Yeah, that's tomorrow, huh?
What if we find something
besides black bass
hanging out at the
bottom of the pond?
[RIRIKO]
Like the matsudodon?
Oh, I almost forgot!
Where there's a drying,
there's overnight dried squid!
I love how everybody's
really getting into
the spirit of this thing!
Overnight dried squid!
Squiddly-diddly-doo!
[YOSHINO]
Well, it's our first drying,
and I officially can't wait!
Me neither!
All right,
but it takes two weeks
for it to completely dry up.
That's going to take a while.
[MINO] It would've been
great if they had coordinated
with us on this so we
could bring in some people.
[YAMADA]
This is so weird.
It's not every day you get to
see Sakura Pond emptied out,
is it?
[SANAE]
Why hasn't it been done?
Mr. Kadota isn't
really keen on it,
at least from what I've heard.
That's right.
Normally I wouldn't be surprised
if he figured out a way to plant
Chupakabura bones at the
bottom of the pond, but--
[MINO]
Shh! He'll hear you!
[DOKUSHIMA] The most
common thing that upsets
nearly every single
foreign tourist
who comes to Japan is the food!
Here's the answer:
I present the Artemis Mark One!
With this incredible device,
anyone can use
chopsticks with ease!
That's not all!
It excels at picking up things
that are normally hard
to get a hold of!
[GROUP]
Oh!
--[YAMADA] That's neat!
--[SHIORI] How cool!
--[door opens]
--[SHIORI] Riichan?
What happened?
Lucia needs our help right away.
Lucia?
You mean the girl here
with the Cryptids?
[RIRIKO]
She has a problem.
A few more of her friends
are coming to town
to see the drying,
so she's hoping you'll help
them find a place to stay.
[SHIORI] I'm amazed
the drying has turned into
this big of a draw.
[RIRIKO]
The Chupakabura lives in water,
so they think they
may find a clue.
The Chupakabura
lives in the water?
There's a long-standing theory
that kappa are
actually Chupakabura.
What's it based on?
Look, can we agree
that any theory
that raises interest in
Manoyama is a good one?
Okay, that's fair.
Who knows, this might even
end up leading to Manoyama
being recognized worldwide!
[MAKI] When do the
other members arrive?
[RIRIKO]
Three days.
[SANAE] That's not much time
but we'll do what we can!
Is something wrong, Yoshino?
I dunno. I was just wondering
whether this is what
the people of Manoyama
actually want.
Meaning, is it good
for rural rejuvenation?
[YOSHINO] I just don't want
to repeat the same mistakes
we made during
the Founding Festival.
No worries, listen up!
They've come all this way
to explore Manoyama,
so let's not overthink it!
Of course we should help them!
Yeah, you're right.
Not just for the town,
but as their Japanese hosts!
Plus, the lack of
lodging in this town
is going to present itself
as a problem over and over
until we address it.
Where have the Cryptids
been staying so far?
Or is this something
I don't wanna know?
They're staying in
one of the empty houses
that an owner has
registered on a B&amp;B site.
As it happens, that's the
only property in Manoyama
that's been properly
registered so far.
All right! Let's check out
some of the other vacant houses
and try to find owners
who'll let people stay!
I'm afraid we can't.
Why? What do you mean?
Even if you do find one,
you still have to apply
for an operating permit
and receive approval,
and that's gonna take
you a month, at least.
Are you kidding?
Can't you just put them up
in a regular inn or a hotel?
They've got places one
town over in Tomikura.
They said they'd really prefer
to stay in an old-style house.
Picky, aren't they?
[YAMADA] We should be
happy they like it here!
It's a lot better than
the alternative!
What if you didn't take
any money for the rent?
Genius!
If it's free, then the
hospitality industry laws
don't apply!
We have the old list
we made of empty homes.
We can hit them
up one at a time!
[ANGELICA] So, this is
the one you found, huh?
[YOSHINO]
Yep! It wasn't that hard.
[SHIORI] We're going to go
clean it up right now!
Oh, that works out perfectly!
Please put this in the entryway.
Why a gold shachi-hoko?
It's for the feng-shui.
[YOSHINO]
This house is impressive.
[SANAE]
Even if we have to clean it,
letting them stay for free
was very generous!
[MAKI] Well, they were
probably just maintaining it,
so maybe they're happy that
it gets to be used somehow.
[SHIORI] If this goes well,
the owners said
they'll think seriously
about applying
for registration as
an official B&amp;B!
Okay!
Let's show 'em how
well we can clean up
and get this place
under control!
[knocking]
[RIRIKO]
Lucia?
Cómo estás, Ririko?
I will help! Okay, yes?
[DOKUSHIMA]
What's on your mind?
Thought you gave up on
that dream a long time ago.
It must've fallen apart by now.
[USHIMATSU] It's always there
in my mind, though.
[YOSHINO] Good work, guys!
We did great!
[GROUP chattering]
Que bonito!
[LUCIA speaking Spanish]
Look, Ririko!
This is Wenbu Lake in Tibet.
Sharipovo village in Russia.
Stour River in England.
Oh, look!
This is Africa.
I took some pictures with
Mandinka people from Senegal.
[YOSHINO]
Kadota and Doku!
[MAKI] Wonder what
they're pondering over.
[RIRIKO]
Grandma.
Hmm? What is it?
Have you ever had a
moment when you felt like
you wanted to leave Manoyama?
I've never even
thought about it.
Why are you asking me
this right now?
I guess because I've
never thought about it, either.
[SERGIO]
Hola! [speaking Spanish]
Yoshi, did you
notice their shirts?
Oh, they actually
went and had them fixed!
[SHIORI] I think the people in
town will be a bit relieved!
[SERGIO speaking Spanish]
[GROUP chattering]
Shall we live there together?
In the big, empty casa
of my corazon?
Perdón?
Por favor, tu boda me?
What the hell?
Are you proposing to her?
Shut up! You should talk!
What the hell is that?
Don't look... at my mouth.
It's him.
[CRYPTID E]
Vale.
[USHIMATSU]
I'm gonna head home.
I'll leave the rest
of it to you.
[SHIORI]
See you later, Mr. Kadota!
[SERGIO]
Adios.
Oh, hey, by the way, Doku.
I saw you and Mr. Kadota
standing on the path
by the pond.
So?
You both seemed like you
were in kind of a reverie.
What were you talking about?
Oh.
Just two old fools
trading ghost stories.
[laughs]
[YOSHINO chuckles]
[USHIMATSU]
Hm?
[gasps] No!
This is bad,
oh jeez, this is bad!
[GROUP chattering]
[SERGIO]
Huh? Huh?!
[speaking Spanish]
[CARLOS]
Todos a sus puestos!
[CRYPTIDS]
Sí, señor. Venga! Vamos!
[YOSHINO]
What? Where're they going?
No way!
Could it really be the
water-dwelling Chupakabura?
[DOKUSHIMA]
Huh?
No! It's Ushimatsu!
[GROUP gasps]
He's drowning?
Let's save him!
Outta the way!
Look, mi amor!
[SANDAL] No, leave it to me,
I've got this covered!
We need an ambulance
at Sakura Pond right away!
[KINU]
I'm so sorry.
He's really put you girls
through a whole lot of trouble.
[YOSHINO] It's fine.
We're just so glad he's okay.
I wonder what
could've happened
to make him jump
in the pond at night.
Hard to say.
[MAKI] Maybe he was planting
Chupakabura bones or something.
Then he would've at least
worn a bathing suit.
I mean, even Mr. Kadota
isn't stupid enough
to jump purposefully
into the pond
with all his clothes on.
Well, then, perhaps
something inside the pond
pulled him down into it!
Don't say that!
[DOKUSHIMA] Just two old
fools trading ghost stories.
Ghost stories.
[RIRIKO] Have you ever had
a moment when you felt like
you wanted to leave Manoyama?
[phone ringing]
What would someone
call about this late?
[CHITOSE]
What?
Ushimatsu was drowning
in Sakura Pond?
[DOKUSHIMA]
Yeah.
The thing from fifty
years ago is back.
[CHITOSE] You called just to
tell me about that nonsense?
You called me at
this hour for that?
That thing...
I can't reveal that thing's
existence to everyone!
I can't do it!
I can't!
[SANDAL] I thought I'd be so
concerned about the secret
in Sakura Pond that I
wouldn't be able to sleep,
but I actually
slept really well.
Next time:
"The Harlequin on the Pond."