[gasps]
[YOSHINO]
Maki!
So, yeah, about earlier--
Forget it! Come with me!
Huh?
Actually, Takeshi asked me
to hold onto this for him
before he left.
[MOE]
Is that--?
He said that, if something
were to happen to him,
I would need to, uh--
[SONODA]
Cut! Let's do it again!
[FIRST ASST DIRECTOR 6A]
All right, stop camera.
Everyone, get reset.
Yoshi's back.
[SONODA]
That was the a 17th take!
Who hired this total amateur?
Sorry, sir.
This isn't going
very well, is it?
I guess I'll give it a try.
Hold on.
If you switch it up now,
they'll have to call in
costume and makeup
and everything.
They'll lose time
and get even angrier.
So what are we supposed to do?
We're in this situation
because of you!
I know, and I apologize
for that. But, still--
[CHIEF ASSISTANT DIRECTOR]
'Kay, if everyone's ready,
we'll start! Rolling!
[SONODA]
And, action!
Actually, Takeshta asked me to--
[SONODA]
Cut!
--Why? Why do you torture me?
--[YOSHINO] Poor Rii- chan ,
I feel so bad for her!
His name's Takeshi.
But, don't worry!
Try to be calm.
[RIRIKO] Takeshi, Takeshi,
Takeshi, Takeshi, Takeshi,
Takeshi, Takeshi,
Takeshi, Takeshi.
All right. I'll do it.
Let them know.
No, I can't.
What is wrong with you?
If I take over now,
Rii- chan will always be afraid
of performing in
front of people.
[MAKI] Hey, think you
could gimme a second?
Sorry to interrupt.
It's no problem.
Okay, break a leg!
Okay, quiet on set!
And, action!
Actually, Takeshi asked me
to hold onto this for him
before he left.
[MOE]
Is that...?
He said that, if something
were to happen to him,
I should give it to you.
[MOE gasps]
Oh, Takeshi.
[SONODA]
Cut! Finally!
[GROUP gasps]
Wow, what'd you say
to her over there?
Nothing much.
Hey, you okay?
You did a great job!
I don't know, but thank you.
And another successful day
down in the books!
Hey, look!
Congratulations, Boss man,
you're a star!
[gasps]
[BOTH]
You're gonna win a Razzie!
Will you shut up?
What? We can't do that--
it's way too sudden!
I'm really sorry it's so tight,
but I know you can do it!
Yeah, I'm coming!
So, Queen, can I count on you?
I promise to try.
I can ask around.
What's going on?
Is the director throwing
another tantrum?
It's worse.
It's supposed to rain today,
so they've decided to film
the indoor scenes a day
ahead of schedule.
They want to do
tomorrow's indoor scenes?
Sure do.
Mini zombies.
What? Oh, that's right!
Tomorrow, the zombies are
all played by children!
There are 20
mini zombies in all.
We've only just
gotten them booked.
[SANAE] We can't very well
expect them to come today
when we just finished
booking them for tomorrow.
But we've gotta figure
out something, right?
Hey, how old should
these mini zombies be?
Early elementary school or so.
It's possible I may
have a solution.
For real?
Great, so I guess
we'll leave it to you.
On it.
Ririko and I will be ready
with a back up plan.
Sure thing.
[YOSHINO]
I'll come with you!
Maybe focus on the house?
[YOSHINO]
Crap. You're so right.
I mean, you've only
got three days left.
[YOSHINO]
But what can I do?
Shiori says she still
can't find the owners.
You'll figure it out.
Just keep at it!
[YOSHINO]
Okay. Thanks for the push.
[YOSHINO] I still doubt
I'll get through, though.
[phone ringing]
Oh, hi! Uh, is this Ms.--
Is this Ms. Yasuda?
I'm Yoshino Koharu and I'm with
the Manoyama Tourism Board.
[KOSUKE]
Wha...?
Me? Why?
Why do you think, weirdo?
You work with kids!
The Dondoko Taiko Club?
All right, fine, I'll try,
but I make no promises
for more than a few.
[MAKI]
We'll take what we can get.
I'm counting on you!
You owe me a popsicle.
So, that's done and done.
--[YOSHINO panting]
--[MAKI gasps]
I'm fine, thanks!
[ROUBA] "And so, the little
girl said to the wolf,
'Why, grandmother what big teeth
and what a big mouth
you have, there!'
And then, the wolf
carefully replied,
'Well, my dear,
sometimes I like to
unhinge my jaw for fun!'
That's not how it goes!
--Aw!
--[SHIORI giggles]
Well, well, Little Shi
is growing up.
Yay, I'm big!
And next year,
you'll be even bigger.
[gasps]
Hey, Yoshi.
Just tell me. Why did
you lie, Shiori?
[gasps]
[YOSHINO] I called and
talked to the owners.
They were confused
because they said
they already gave us
permission a while ago.
You met with them
in person, didn't you?
I'll try and explain.
I spent a lot of time in
this house, growing up.
There was a sweet
old woman who lived here.
She passed away a while back,
but this place still holds a lot
of special childhood
memories for me.
When they said they
wanted to burn it down
for the movie,
it really hit me hard.
A house isn't merely
a pile of wood.
It's full of the
lives and memories
of the people who lived there.
But what about the movie?
They brought their entire
shoot here under the condition
that they'd be able
to use a house.
Think how much the movie
will do for the town!
Yeah, I know that, but, I--
When I started trying to
find a replacement house,
you didn't seem to have
a problem with that.
So you don't care
about the memories
people have of
those other houses?
You don't mind burning houses
that have nothing
to do with you.
I never said that!
Look, I understand how you feel,
but you can't live in the past!
You have to look forward.
[SHIORI]
You don't...
You don't know!
How could someone who abandoned
their hometown understand?
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Hey! Eating alone today?
I know you're workin'
hard. Hang in there.
Thanks, I'm trying
my best to do that.
Uh... Uh-oh.
[CHILDREN chattering]
Look how many little zombies!
You're the best.
It wasn't me.
[MAKI]
Hm?
Dad used the school's old
emergency contact phone tree.
[gasps]
You'd better thank him.
Yeah, whatever. I didn't
ask for his help.
I'm taking a walk.
I don't wanna run into him.
I had no idea the
Oden Minister's dad
was the vice principal here!
Wonder what he's like.
He's here now.
Where is he?
Over there.
[SANAE]
Woah. He looks super intense.
[BOY 7A] You're so stupid!
I'm the very scariest!
[BOY 7B]
Nuh-uh!
You're just a crappy
zombie that gets killed!
No way! That's you!
--You're the crappiest!
--[SANAE] Hey, guys,
we're about to get started,
so let's quiet down, okay--
Oh!
Shut up, four-eyes big-butt!
[CHILDREN] Big butt!
Big butt! Big butt! Big butt!
--[SANAE] Wh-What?
--Big butt! Big butt!
Big butt! Big butt!
Okay, guys! Are we ready
to have fun today?
[CHILDREN]
Yeah!
They're mini monsters!
This takes me back.
Hey.
I'm bad with kids.
Oh, really?
[RIRIKO]
This book is still here, though.
Guess you went to
this school, too, huh?
[RIRIKO]
Yes.
I started when you
were in sixth grade.
Oh, wow.
[RIRIKO]
Uh, so. Um...
Thanks for helping me
the other day.
[MAKI]
That? Sure.
It's okay. It's not a big deal.
But, I--
Acting is living in
an imaginary situation.
Don't think about
the performance.
Just be present in
that moment in time.
It really can be as
simple as that. Cool?
Yeah.
So? How was it?
Did you end up
enjoying it at all?
[RIRIKO]
Mm...
Hey! They're still
doing the same show!
That's crazy!
[RIRIKO]
You mean Snow White ?
[MAKI]
Yep, we did it, too.
I lost at rock-paper-scissors
and didn't get to
play Snow White.
There were so many
students back in the day.
Oh! There I am!
Look at that, I played
a tree. A tree!
[MAKI chuckles]
I remember one year,
there was a girl
with a huge smile that was the
most graceful tree I ever saw.
Bet it was you.
In truth, it probably was.
So you've liked acting
since you were a little kid?
Yeah, I guess.
[MAKI]
Hey, here's a tip.
You've gotta do
more than "like" it
or you won't get far,
kid. Trust me.
[MOE]
Please, wake up, Takeshi!
You have to wake up!
I love you, and I know
you love me, too!
You have to remember
what we said! Stop!
[groans]
Cut! That'll work!
Still not really
following the plot, here.
Basically, the house
is a special place
that links our reality
to an alternate one.
So they're going to burn
the whole house down
to block off the entrance?
Yeah, I don't get it at all.
I was really feeling that scene!
You nailed it, Moe!
Oh, thanks so much!
It was important
to me to show her
struggling with
her love, you know?
I'm sorry about before.
I think I kinda lost it.
What I said was really mean.
No worries. I should
apologize, too.
You're just trying to do your
job. I made it harder for you.
[YOSHINO]
It's okay.
You sure you're fine
about the house?
It doesn't really matter,
when it comes down to it.
It was never my
decision to make.
But it did occur to me
that she might've actually
liked this--having the house
preserved in this movie,
rather than it just
being forgotten.
I mean, I hope so.
[FUJIWARA]
Okay, let's take five, everyone!
Once the sun goes down,
we'll start shooting
the final scene!
Everybody be ready!
Romeo! Oh, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou?
Wherefore art thou, Romeo?
[ANGELICA]
If it's the sun card,
you'll continue
to pursue acting.
But if you choose
the Reaper card,
you'll give it up, completely.
Make sure you choose carefully.
[door bell rings]
[KOSUKE]
Ah, there you are.
Oh, hey, Kosuke.
That's right, I owe
you a melon popsicle.
--Do you want it?
--[KOSUKE] Nah, it's fine.
For you. It's from Dad.
Uh-- What is it?
He said you'll know it
when you see it.
[ANGELICA]
Want to watch it?
Please, I'm lost.
[MAKI]
Is this Snow White ?
Come this way!
[KOSUKE]
Sure is.
Dad was in charge of filming
school events back then.
[KOSUKE]
You're really graceful!
Yeah, I guess I was.
Apparently, the principal
was pretty pissed off.
He chewed Dad out.
Because he didn't film any
of the other kids at all.
Huh?
I see.
Who woulda thought?
Seems to me you've found
your very first fan.
[FILM CREW 7E] You guys have
fed us really well this week!
Thanks so much!
What? Fukuragi is yellowtail?
Baby ones.
[SHIORI]
We've got plenty of food here!
Don't be afraid to get seconds!
[FUJIWARA]
What? Are you serious?
[SONODA]
Come on, they're in love!
Takeshi is stuck inside
a burning house.
You don't think it's
weird that she'd just
sit outside and scream instead
of going in after him?
She should fling
herself inside! Dive in!
Oh, yeah, I totally get it.
But at this point,
it's hard to change it.
[SONODA] It doesn't matter
how difficult it is!
The plot is a living thing,
it's a living thing!
You've got to be kidding.
Agreed. I want to
shoot it that way.
Well, now! Atta girl!
That's the spirit!
Moe, you really shouldn't make
these decisions on your own!
But don't you think it's
only natural for her
to want to be with the one
she loves until the very end?
I can't let you to do
something this dangerous.
I'm sorry.
The company's made
a big investment in you
and there's nobody else
to take your place.
But I really want to do it.
[MAKI]
I can take Moe's place.
[MOE]
Maki?
What's she doing?
Maki, no.
I know I'm a bit taller,
but if we shoot from
behind, you can't tell.
Uh, wait, who are you?
--Stand-in?
--[MOE] It's dangerous, though.
Really.
Please let me do this, okay?
It's not every day an
opportunity comes along.
Yeah, all right.
That's what I'm talkin'
about! Let's get to it!
Maki, are you sure this is okay?
What if something
were to happen?
I love it.
This is the thing
I love to do most.
I can't ignore it anymore.
Everyone! I'm excited
to work with you.
[FUJIWARA] Okay, if you're
done with dinner,
we could use help digging!
[FILM CREW 7F] Try to project
the sound in that direction.
I'll give the signal...
[TOWNSPEOPLE chattering]
[FILM CREW 7H]
Once you've moved that...
[CHIEF ASSISTANT DIRECTOR 7A]
Okay, the director says
he wants us to move
two meters to the right.
Okay, so, you're going
to run over this way,
and then jump into
that hole, right there.
There is a fire
truck standing by,
so if things get really
dangerous, we'll stop shooting.
Cool. I'm ready when you are.
Number one is go!
[FILM CREW 7L]
Two is go!
[FILM CREW 7M]
Three is go!
[FILM CREW 7N] The average
wind speed is zero point five.
[FILM CREW 7P]
Everyone standby!
[FILM CREW 7Q]
Lights off!
Just one shot!
So let's get this one right!
[FILM CREW]
Yes, sir!
We're rolling!
Stand by.
Action!
Takeshi, no!
And, cut! Okay!
Maki, you were
absolutely perfect!
You play me better
than I play myself!
Thanks, it really had been
a while. It felt good!
[ISOGAI] Moe! They've got
a bouquet for you!
'Kay!
I hope we get to work together
again sometime soon!
I'll see you around!
[YOSHINO]
Maki! You okay?
You didn't hurt
yourself, did you?
Nope.
[sighs] I'm just so relieved
you're back safe and sound!
You really are a genuinely
kind soul, aren't you?
Uh... I don't know--
Thanks, Yoshi. So much.
Huh? I didn't do
anything, though.
Wow, it all happened so quickly!
[TOWNSPERSON 7C]
That was quite a show!
Okay, everyone,
that's scene 112!
So, on behalf of Sonoda's
entire crew, that's a wrap!
Thanks so much for
all your hard work!
[FILM CREW chattering]
[FUJIWARA]
Ms. Shinomiya!
[pants] You've been such
an incredible help.
If we hadn't had everyone's
wonderful support,
this shoot would
have been a disaster.
Thank you!
Not at all.
It's rare that
people on location
go this far to help us.
I'm starting on
another shoot soon,
and I'll be sure to tell
everyone about this place.
Oh, really? I appreciate that.
You know, I've been
kinda wondering
if the Queen might have
had some kind of attachment
to that house.
Sorry?
[FUJIWARA]
Oh. You didn't hear?
About this?
It's the woman that
used to live here.
The Queen asked us
to be sure to give her
a special mention and thanks
in the end credits.
What?
[FUJIWARA] She said we
should value the memory
of the person that lived here...
That a house is more than
just a pile of wood.
Come visit again,
okay! Take care!
[YOSHINO] Great job!
We actually pulled it off!
To us!
[MAKI, SANAE, RIRIKO, SHIORI]
I mean, we had to
deal with a lot of stuff,
but thanks to everyone's
sheer brilliance,
we did it, 'n this beer's good!
It's weird, everyone
left so quickly.
They hardly said anything.
I thought we'd at least
have a little wrap party.
I guess it really
was low budget, huh?
But what matters is that
now we're building up
a really good reputation,
and that might help us
bring the town back to life!
Welcome to Zombie Town.
Ah!
Maki, what you did
was really cool.
Wow. Thanks, lady.
Although I did have
some great people
supporting me and stuff.
It's nice to be home, isn't it?
Yeah. It was good to run
into the younger me.
You're always welcome here!
That's just the kind
of town Manoyama is.
[SANAE]
What kind, exactly?
I wish more people would
run away to see us.
Hear, hear.
I'm going to run away, too.
No! You're gonna
stay right here!
With me.
[chuckles] Uh-oh, say something
to your Minister, Queen.
Are you asleep?
[laughs] At least put
your beer down first.
Jeez, she has a vice
grip on this thing!
She won't let go!
[RIRIKO]
Rigor mortis.
[SANAE]
Hey, don't kill her off.
[MAKI] Like, "Time of
death: 12 hours ago."
[SANAE]
The Oden Detective is back!
[SHIORI]
Yoshi! Yoshi!
What's up?
You won't believe it--
it's a movie production
company from Tokyo!
Seriously? So, Mr. Fujiwara
kept his promise!
They said they wanna
speak to the Queen.
[gasps]
Yes. Hello!
This is Yoshino Koharu,
Queen of the kingdom
of Chupakabura,
[MOVIE PRODUCER 7A] So,
I heard from this guy I know.
Is it true that in Manoyama
you can shoot car chases
and blow up temples if you want?
Huh?
[MOVIE PRODUCER 7A]
If it's true, we'd love to shoot
a big-time, knock-your-socks-off
movie in your town!
I really think he might
have oversold us.
[SANDAL] The movie
wrapped, but apparently,
my scene was cut.
Boo.
Mr. Sonoda, you're fired.
Next time: "The Fairy's Recipe."