[CHITOSE]
Well, Shi.
Do you really think
you can do that?
Yes I can. I will lift
this burden off the Queen.
And I will commit to take
the lead on this project.
[SHIORI]
I'm still shaking like a leaf!
And to think how
reluctant you've been
to take a leadership
role before now.
Trust me, no one's more
surprised than I am.
But all I could think about was
how to save Yoshi
from that situation.
I feel terrible, Shiori.
No worries, Queen, I insist.
I wonder if Rii- chan is okay.
[CHITOSE]
So, did you really not know?
You had no clue it was on the
same date as our festival?
No, I didn't.
Unbelievable. Your head
is in the clouds, girl.
No, I just don't care.
[MAKI]
I'm gonna have the somen .
Yeah, me, too!
Again?
You guys are quite the
somen enthusiasts, huh?
[TAKAMIZAWA]
So, what's wrong with that?
I've been eating somen
since childhood.
That's just how it
is here in Manoyama.
But why? What is
it about somen ?
Is it because we
harvest so much wheat?
It's because 50 percent of
our bodies are made of somen .
[SANAE]
Oh, stop. Be real, please.
[SHIORI]
Hey, Sandal, what did you order
for dinner tonight?
I'm having borscht.
[YOSHINO]
You're eating borscht?
Wait, does that mean
you come from Russia?
Nope, it doesn't.
[YOSHINO]
Where are you from, then?
Where's your hometown?
Oh, you know what they say,
"When the home's far away,
you stink about it."
Don't you mean
"think" about it?
[SANAE] Look at that, they even
put somen in their borscht.
It's just a little
cultural exchange.
People love their hometowns.
That's it!
[knocking]
Hey, Shiori, think you
might want this bag?
Huh? You sure?
I thought this was
one of your favorites!
Yep, so take good care of it.
Still working hard, I see?
[SHIORI]
Mm-hm.
[SAYURI] Just don't wear
yourself out, all right?
[YAMADA] The Manoyama Somen
Mega Expo. I get it.
You're partnering it up
with the Board of Merchants'
summer festival, right?
Yeah! Somen is a
Manoyama specialty,
locally produced and
locally consumed.
So that part, at least,
should make the Board
of Merchants happy.
This isn't just a simple
presentation, either.
It's a contest!
We'll have different
organizations
run competing booths,
and the winner will be
decided by the guests' votes.
[SANAE] Anyone who lives
in Manoyama can participate.
Showcasing people's unique
ways of serving somen
is a cool way to showcase
the town, itself!
[MAKI] The winning dish will
be made an official recipe
of the kingdom, and we're
in talks to have it served
at the city hall cafeteria.
Huh. That's not half bad.
Really? You think so?
It allows the Board of
Merchants to save face, too.
And I like that it's
open participation.
Yeah, but, I still
don't think it's gonna
be enough to change
the old hag's mind.
[MINO] Why don't we add
something to make it beneficial
for them in some way?
Yeah, that's good.
Something like holding a
farmer's market alongside it?
Yes, we can invite local vendors
and other producers, too!
It's a total win-win!
Okay, we'll go ahead
and update our proposal!
[CHITOSE] Interesting plan.
You've worked hard, here.
I have no objections
to what you propose.
[BOTH gasp]
Thank you so much, ma'am!
I hope you know
that I didn't say
any of those things because
I have a problem with you.
I just need you to help support
the Board of Merchants.
[YOSHINO] Of course!
We'll be more careful.
Shiori, thank you.
Oh! We have one more
favor to ask of you.
What is it?
[SHIORI] Would you give
Rii- chan your blessing
to be a member of our
team on this project?
All five of us
worked on it together.
If you took one of us
out of the equation,
it wouldn't be our
project anymore.
All right, then.
[gasps]
Oh, yay!
[CHITOSE]
Be warned.
The Board of Merchants is
going to win this contest.
[CHEF 9A]
A somen competition?
That actually sounds
like a lot of fun!
We'll give it a shot!
[YOSHINO]
Thank you so much!
We got the Mommies
Together Club!
So far, so good.
That's right!
And it's all thanks to
Shiori's super-smart plan.
[USHIMATSU]
Hm?
I don't know, it just
seems to me that Shiori's
got a real knack for mediating.
Well, that's just because locals
have a unique way
of interacting.
That doesn't mean outsiders
should get discouraged, though.
Uh--
What I'm saying is,
you don't need to get upset
just because you
screwed up a little bit.
Ah. So, you could tell, huh?
The Queen has no time to
stand around, navel-gazing!
She must keep moving forward!
So forward we go!
Right!
[USHIMATSU]
Forge on, straight ahead!
Straight ahead, and then
take a right at the T!
[YOSHINO]
Got it!
[USHIMATSU]
Her cup runneth over.
You know somethin'?
This is a pretty solid
project, coming from you.
I would've been more
aggressive, though.
[YOSHINO]
So, um.
How exactly do you two
fellas know each other?
Well, we used to
build stuff together
when we were much younger.
No, I was your
glorified lab rat!
There was this crazy Icarus
Project where he put these
weird wings on me and
pushed me off a cliff.
I bestowed the gift
of flight upon him!
Almost killed me,
is what you did!
[YOSHINO]
That's messed up.
All right. Gimme a
booth at this thingy.
I'll call it "Doku's Booth."
That's catchy.
[laughs]
[SHIORI]
Thanks!
We appreciate you
letting us put a poster up.
[KUMANO]
No problem at all!
An expo for somen
is a really solid idea!
Man, something smells so good!
Oh, I was just making myself
a little somethin' back there.
You want some?
Holy wow!
I've never in my life had
French toast this good!
Oh, thank you.
To tell you the truth,
this stuff is responsible
for changing my life,
for better or for worse.
[GIRLS]
Huh?
[KUMANO]
It was back in high school.
I took a cooking class and
we were making egg dishes.
Hey, Kumano, what'd
you decide to make?
Oh, Shinomiya!
Um, it's only some French toast.
Ah! I love French toast!
Can I try a bite?
[KUMANO]
U-Uh, sure.
It's scrumptious! I'm
really impressed, Kumano!
[KUMANO]
That was when I decided
I'd go to France and study
to perfect my French toast.
Whoa!
That was your only reason
for training in France?
And all this time
I thought that Shiori
was the one you were into.
[SHIORI]
Yeah right! Whatever!
Sayuri's always been
the one, hasn't she?
I admit, all I wanted was
to see her smile again.
However, once I got to France,
I realized something
rather troubling.
Was it the fact
that French toast
didn't even originate in France?
[SANAE, SHIORI, MAKI]
Wha...?
One theory is that
the name of the dish
comes from an American
named Joseph French.
So, French was just
the guy's name?
Some American dude?
[KUMANO]
Yeah. So, that's what happened.
But I couldn't turn
around and go home
just because of
a misunderstanding.
So, before I knew it, I became
a fully trained French chef.
Well, your food is
genius-level good.
[SHIORI] If you really
liked my sister that much,
why on earth didn't you tell her
before you left for France?
Oh, I had planned to!
But she never showed up like
she promised me she would.
She said the exact same
thing to me about you.
[gasps]
[YOSHINO]
Oh, come on.
All you did here was switch
the tea out for broth.
No, I developed a new sensor
that automatically pours more
broth when it gets diluted.
[YOSHINO] Yeah, that's not
what I meant, though.
Isn't there some way to,
like, try to involve the--
[YOSHINO gasps]
Oh, Doku! I think I've got it!
We're about to make
somen so exciting!
What?
[CHIKAKO]
Take care of yourself, okay?
Please try not to work too hard.
[SHIORI] Good luck,
Sayuri! I'll miss you!
[TAKAYUKI sobbing]
My little girl!
Aw, Dad, come on,
it's just one town over.
Okay, bye, everyone!
[yelps]
[panting]
Kumano! Are you okay?
[KUMANO]
Yeah. Shinomiya.
There's something I really
need to talk to you about
before you go away.
What is it?
What's this?
I was under the impression
the chef liked Shiori.
Do you remember what
I said at graduation?
That I'd be waiting
for you at three o'clock
at the station the next Sunday?
[SAYURI]
Mm-hm.
I waited for you there
well into the night.
But, you never showed up.
So, that's why I left
for France before I'd--
But I was waiting, too! I was!
[KUMANO gasps]
[SAYURI] I mean, I waited
most of the night, but...
It was the Sunday right
after graduation, yeah?
Yeah. I don't get it.
[MOVER 9A] Hey! We're ready
to take off if that's okay!
Thank you! Yes, that'll be fine!
Sorry.
I'll come back by for
dinner again, soon.
[SHIORI]
What happened? What'd she say?
[MAKI] Well, maybe it was
the wrong station.
I don't really see how.
Not when there's only
one station in Manoyama.
Then I guess they
must have been waiting
in different places.
Oh, yeah! Like Shibuya Station!
[MAKI] Right, like waiting
at the Moyai statue
instead of Hachiko!
But the difference is,
this station only
has one meet-up spot.
[YOSHINO]
We're back!
[SHIORI]
How'd it go?
Tons of people signed up!
All the booths are full!
That's incredible!
No way, Yoshi! Bet that
was a lotta work!
[YOSHINO]
It actually wasn't!
Everyone was really interested.
Oh! I almost forgot,
I brought you guys a treat
from the Local Cuisine Society!
[SHIORI]
Ooh! My favorite!
I love these!
What are they?
Rice balls covered in
kombu seaweed flakes.
Why cover them?
No idea.
These have been
around here forever.
Makes sense.
I've noticed that
since I've moved here.
People in Manoyama eat
a crazy amount of kombu .
Oh, really?
You use it in broths,
to flavor your sushi
and rice, even kombu tea!
One time, at a pub here,
I even witnessed a guy
drinking kombu liquor.
[MINO] Well, Toyama actually
has the highest kombu
consumption rate per
capita in the country.
It's kinda strange, huh?
It's not like you can
harvest it in Toyama Bay
and Manoyama isn't
close to the sea.
[USHIMATSU]
Back in the Edo Period,
it was common for trade
ships from Hokkaido
to make frequent stops
at each port in the north.
And it so happened that
they brought a lot of kombu
with them when they did.
Oh, well I guess
that answers that.
[SANAE] Learning more about
this place every day.
So true.
We eat these things all the
time without thinking about it,
but they're directly
connected to our history.
And they're good!
Hey, wait a sec.
[MAKI]
What? I see the wheels turning.
We'll come up with
an amazing dish--
something only the Tourism
Board could pull off!
We'll crush the
Board of Merchants!
No, I'm starting to
feel the pressure!
I'll tell you a secret.
I've come up with
a surprise, myself.
[SANAE]
Hm? What is it?
[YOSHINO] Well, it's
directly related to somen ,
and it's completely interactive.
[YOSHINO laughs]
You've got a scary
look on your face.
You good with it, Mr. Kadota?
Of course, I'm totally
good with it.
Bring it on!
[DOKUSHIMA]
You came.
[YOSHINO]
Yes.
All right, let's do it. Doku.
[SHIORI]
Somen and kombu .
I'm so used to them that I
can't see what to do with them.
[SHIORI sighs]
They're just going to say
my idea is boring again!
I wish Sayuri was
here to help me.
Why don't you take
a little break?
[SHIORI] Yoshino and the
others are all working
really hard, so I can't
slack off right now.
Aw! But what if no one from
town even shows up for this?
I mean, what're
we gonna do, then?
You worry about things like this
a little too much, Shiori.
Maybe so.
But I personally got
these people involved,
and we're spending
a lot of money on it.
So, I think about it
being completely empty,
and it scares me.
Because I'll be the one
responsible if it fails.
I'd feel terrible.
I'd wanna disappear.
Yoshino's doing great and
I really do respect her.
I don't know the details here.
But it sounds to me like
you should ask your friends
for a little more help, hm?
Thank you, Mom.
But the problem is,
we've only got one week left.
[gasps] No way! Do I have
the wrong date down?
Oh, no!
[CHIKAKO]
Shiori? What is it?
[SHIORI]
The date!
The date is...
Oh, my gosh, what has
that silly girl done?
It's last year's calendar!
Oh. Are you kidding me?
I think I was
seriously on the verge
of having a heart attack!
[CHIKAKO] You two have
always been such airheads.
I'm so nervous.
Hey, don't worry!
I'm sure folks are
gonna show up.
Look!
So many people!
Look at that, Shiori!
Yeah!
Okay then, what do you
want to do first?
I'm hungry, Mommy!
When do we eat?
[SANAE] Hello, everyone!
We want to welcome you
to the first Manoyama
Somen Mega Expo!
Everything you see in the
booths is free of charge!
There are plenty of
options, so make sure
you save room to
try 'em all, folks!
The booth that receives
the most votes
will be the champion.
We'll promote that
lucky winner's recipe
as one of Manoyama's
specialties!
There's no way we're losing
to the Tourism Board.
[SHIORI]
Our recipe is unique!
Rather than serving
the noodles in a broth,
we've chosen to flavor our
dish with a thicker sauce.
You place the well-strained
somen , in a bowl,
and then you add some
kombu flakes, okra,
natto , and some
grated mountain yam.
Lastly, you're gonna
throw in just a splash
of sauce with sesame oil.
Mix it up, and it's
all ready for you
and your family to enjoy!
Wow! This is good!
[MAKI]
Kosuke, what do you think?
It's making me feel
nostalgic, somehow.
Curious, why kombu ?
[SHIORI] Well, kombu and
somen have been popular
in Manoyama for such
a long time, so,
we thought it made sense
for them to be
considered a local dish.
Guys!
How 'bout a bowl
of Happy Somen ?
It's pretty tasty! Wanna try?
Count me in!
It sounds totally boring.
Well, look at this, though.
Kombu is low in calories
and it contains nutrients
that are said to increase
the size of your bust.
Huh?
[ERIKA]
I'm sold.
[RIRIKO]
Here you go. Enjoy.
There's still time for you, too.
Huh?
[KUMANO]
Shiori! Sorry I'm so late.
I was busy with prep.
[SHIORI]
Hey, Kumano!
Here you go.
Tastes like your
hard work paid off.
And I like the name, too.
Thanks so much, Chef!
I'm hopeful that this
will help us find
some new local
favorites, you know?
Yeah! Oh, I almost forgot.
Try not to miss each
other this time, okay?
I guess they've started
to figure things out.
[SANAE] Ladies and gentlemen,
we're currently
tallying your votes for
the Somen Mega Expo.
We'll have the results soon.
But in the meantime,
let's have a word
from Yoshino Koharu,
Queen of the kingdom
of Chupakabura.
Huh?!
Good afternoon! I hope
you're all having fun!
Yoshi!
What's with the swimsuit?
We've got a lot of great
new somen dishes here today,
but I'd like to show you a cool
new way to experience them!
What new way?
I think we can all agree,
everyone loves somen .
And now, thanks to this guy,
you can get closer to
your favorite noodle!
May I present the brand new,
Over-Flowing Somen 5-DX!
"Overflowing Somen "?
All right, let's eat!
[MACHINE VOICE 9A]
Prepare to overflow!
[YOSHINO]
There it is!
Ah... Ah.
[YOSHINO yells]
Ya see? It stimulates
the five senses!
A 5-DX exper--
In ya go. In ya go. In ya go.
I might need to go ahead
and automate this part, too.
Do you think this was
the "little surprise"
that Yoshi was
bragging about earlier?
You mean this
high-tech masterpiece?
It looks fun.
It's a meal... you enjoy...
...with your whole body.
Best game ever!
[GIRL 9A]
I wanna play, too, Mommy!
[YAMADA]
Here, Kozuki!
Take it! Hurry!
Well, everyone,
we hope you enjoyed
that little show.
Now it's time to
announce the results!
The winner of the first
Manoyama Somen Mega Expo is...
The Manoyama Mommies
Together Club
with their Spicy
Somen Spring Rolls!
Congratulations!
Hey, you guys! We did it!
So, I guess we lost.
Aw, it's okay.
I have every intention
of finishing this later.
Well, it was obvious that
we were ahead, anyway.
Shut up, hag!
Come on, now!
Everyone had a good time,
isn't that what counts?
Excuse me, miss,
you're with the
Tourism Board, right?
Yes, I am.
Well, I wanted you to know,
I just loved the Happy Somen .
You think I could serve
it in my restaurant?
[SHIORI]
Yes, of course!
[ROBA]
I really enjoyed it, too!
The flavor was somehow calming.
I'm planning on
making it at home.
[SHIORI]
Please do!
You did so great, Shii- chan .
Well, it's 4PM and I'm
at the throne room.
[SAYURI]
Kumano?
[KUMANO] Shinomiya!
What're you doing here?
Shiori said I had
to be here today.
So weird.
She gave me a note telling me
to be here at four o'clock.
And she gave me this.
[SAYURI]
I think that's from my room.
[KUMANO] Why a calendar?
And it's last year's.
[SAYURI gasps]
That means the calendar
I was looking at
when we were supposed to meet...
It was probably
the wrong one, too!
[gasps]
[SAYURI] I bet I was waiting
for you at the station
on the wrong day!
[gasps]
[laughs]
Well, at least the
mystery's been solved, then!
Oh, man.
I'm so sorry, I guess
I really am an airhead!
Look, why don't we try again?
Will you come back by my
restaurant sometime tomorrow?
I'll even make your
very favorite dish.
You mean that
yummy French toast?
Yep, that recipe
hasn't changed at all!
[BOTH laugh]
[SHIORI]
Oh, there you are, Yoshi!
We've been looking for you.
[MAKI] Hey, don't let it
get you down, girl.
That little show of yours
was remarkably entertaining.
C'mon, don't say that.
I was really trying.
[SANAE]
Aw, you are such mess.
[SHIORI]
Sometimes I envy you, Yoshi.
You've got such a totally
weird imagination!
Not a compliment!
[SANAE] Our dear Yoshino
who never thinks
a single thing through.
And Shiori, who
overthinks everything.
[SANAE laughs] Maybe we should
just add you together
and divide by two.
Okay, from now on,
I swear I'll think things
through completely before I act!
No, wait!
That's not who you are, Yoshi!
I think you should double down,
and go for everything!
And no worries,
'cause I've got your back!
Ah! That's it! An inauguration!
Inauguration?
[RIRIKO] You're the only
one without a title.
Oh! Am I, really?
Lord Shiori Shinomiya,
I hereby declare
that henceforth,
you are known as the
Minister of Mediation!
--Of mediation?
--[YOSHINO] Yeah!
[SANAE]
What's that?
A minster that mediates things
and makes them all good!
Too long.
I humbly submit my resignation.
[YOSHINO]
What?
[RIRIKO]
That was a three-second term.
But why? Don't you like it?
Well, no, it's actually
pretty terrible.
[SANAE]
Girls, whaddya think?
Should we start a revolt? Yeah!
--[SHIORI] Yeah!
--[MAKI] Hear, hear!
[YOSHINO]
Come on, you guys!
[ANGELICA]
Have a seat.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
You know what I want.
[SANDAL] I tried taking
Doku's place at the controls
of the Over-Flowing Somen 5-DX.
That thing wore me out.
Next time: "The
Dragon's Soft Spot."