[SENIORS]
Hey, hey, ho!
[phone ringing]
Hey, Sanae.
[SANAE]
What the hell are you doing?
Being a hostage, basically.
A hostage?!
Please tell me they
haven't got you tied up
or anything.
[YOSHINO] No, it's not like
I'm here against my will.
[SANAE] Okay, whatever,
just get back here.
No way!
Come on, this is
the first time anyone
has really needed me!
I'm a hostage and
I'm gonna play the part!
--Are you nuts? Yoshino?
--[dial tone]
What's going on?
Well, I think we've been had.
What?
This whole time,
the professor's been using us
for his own gain.
This is what he's
really been after.
An at-home coup d'état.
That's right.
He wants to use our livestream
to call attention to the
sad state of Warabiya.
I will now state our demands.
First, I want you to send
a real cameraman
to cover our protest here.
I would also like
three cases of beer
and some snacks.
And if possible,
a single malt whiskey,
which I'll pay for.
He's actually making demands.
Giving them some beer
isn't that big a deal, right?
I'm not sure that's
the problem here.
Look.
We're getting some comments.
[SHIORI] Yoshi doesn't seem
to care about giving
a bad impression.
[MAKI] That was a pretty
mean thing to say, Shiori.
[YOSHINO] Hey, everyone,
the tea is ready!
She seems right
at home, doesn't she?
Anyhow, we've gotta do something
before it gets
negative attention.
Okay.
Oh, I think I've
forgotten my meds.
Well, go get 'em.
We're not in any big rush.
All right, we'll go
ahead to Shige's, then.
[MASA]
Okay.
We'll see you later,
right, fair Queen?
Roger that!
Nobody's gonna take
away our bus route!
[GORO]
I think that about does it!
[MICHIYO]
We really appreciate it, Queen.
This should hold
us over for a while!
You're a very hardworking
hostage, aren't you?
Not at all!
But hey, what exactly do
we do from this point on?
We're committing treason.
But we're not going to do
anything illegal, though.
Well, not for now, anyway.
[GROUP]
Cheers!
I'm sorry about earlier today.
Didn't mean what I said.
No, I was being childish.
I've got some good
fertilizer for you, buddy.
C'mon, Queen,
have a little bit more!
Thanks, yeah, I'll have more.
But Professor, are you
sure this is the best way?
[SUZUHARA chuckles]
Nobody would ever
pay any attention to us
if all we chose to do
was pout and whine
over our lot.
People are drawn to drama.
[HIDE] Seems like you're
always up to something, Masa.
[MASA] The girl with the glasses
is totally my type, though.
[MAKI]
Excuse me!
Maki!
[MAKI] I come to you bearing
gifts of beer and snacks.
Everyone!
The beer and stuff is here!
Was the store open?
Hey, listen.
Have you really
thought this through?
Sanae was pretty upset.
It's got nothing to do
with the tourism board though.
I'm staying up here completely
of my own free will.
I just really want
to stand with them
and help them out.
Cool. I get that.
[SHIGE]
Hey, it's the Oden Detective!
Oh! Yes it is.
No kidding! Come on in
and drink with us!
Sorry, I can't, I'm driving.
[YOSHINO] You could always
just spend the night.
Come on, how about it?
We just opened a bottle,
but of course,
it might be wasted on tanukis.
--[MAKI laughing]
--[GROUP chattering]
[SHIORI] It kinda looks like our
hunter has become the prey,
doesn't it?
[water sloshes]
Ah! This is perfect.
[KIYO] I'm leaving a change
of clothes here for you.
[YOSHINO]
Okay! Thank you so much!
[MASA yells]
[YOSHINO yells]
[YOSHINO]
Wh-What was that?
[MAKI]
It's okay, don't worry!
Just had to scare off a
disgusting ape, that's all.
[CHITOSE]
Ririko.
You're going to Warabiya
village, aren't you?
Yes. I'm the cameraman.
[CHITOSE] I like that old
professor out there.
He has guts.
You take him this gift from
the Board of Merchants, okay?
Good morning, everybody!
--[MINO] G'morning!
--[USHIMATSU] Hey.
Morning, Shiori!
So, how is our
fair queen today?
Yeah, seriously,
what is she doing, anyway?
I'm so sorry.
I know she's making
the Kingdom of Chupakabura
look really bad.
[USHIMATSU]
There's opportunity in crisis!
We'll just flip it,
and the queen's name
will be known across
the whole country!
Here you go!
Give this to the professor!
Last stop, ladies and gents.
Warabiya, Warabiya--
What in the hell?!
[SANAE]
The Republic of Warabiya?
Hey, you guys,
do you know what's
going on with all this?
Uh, kinda.
[KANEDA]
Come on, now, Professor!
You know I can't have this.
Blocking the street?
It's not safe!
[SUZUHARA] Kindaichi,
you and I both know cars
hardly ever use it.
And we're not really
blocking anything.
[DOKU]
Oh, it's the delivery!
If the sensor detects
an approaching car,
it'll automatically
move us off to the side.
You're a pain in the ass!
We just want to
declare our withdrawal
from the Kingdom of Chupakabura.
Simple as that.
I don't think we're bothering
anyone out here, do you?
[KANEDA] You may
say that, but actually...
What is even
the point anymore?
Oh, I give up.
Hi, everyone!
[SHIORI] A gift from the
outside, from Mr. Kadota.
[RIRIKO] I'm going to
be your cameraman.
Also, this is from the
Board of Merchants.
[YOSHINO]
Ooh, thank you!
All right,
I'm heading back for a bit.
Yoshino, are we good?
Yeah, of course!
Sorry about yesterday.
I was actually about to
go mushroom gathering
with the ladies.
Any of you girls wanna come?
Totally!
It's my job, so...
I think I might...
[MAKI] Yeah.
Wanna head back together?
[SUZUHARA] Would you
like some tea, Mr. Kindaichi?
[KANEDA]
No, I can't, I'm on duty.
You're just as uptight
as ever, aren't ya?
Only pick the mushrooms
we showed you, okay?
Right!
There were a
whole bunch of them!
Wow, that's awesome, Yoshi!
[YOSHINO laughs]
[KIYO]
Oh, those are tsukiyotake.
If you eat one of those,
you'll turn ugly and die!
Wha--?
[YOSHINO]
But they look exactly the same!
I wonder how they
tell the difference.
[SUZUHARA] We can get
just about everything we need
from the internet now.
Withstanding a siege isn't
as hard as one might think.
[SANAE] But you know
you can't do it forever.
Professor, how long
are you planning
for this to continue?
What's your end game? What's the
goal you're working towards?
I'm doing this to make
the people of Manoyama
aware of this problem.
And, look--our supporters
are increasing.
I guess.
Still, I just wonder
if you're actually going
to solve anything.
[SUZUHARA]
I can understand that.
But, this village will
disappear, eventually.
I just wanted to
be able to document
a bit of their culture
before that happens.
Today I'm going to
show you folks
how to prepare Warabiya soba.
The most important
ingredient for this is water.
You can't make a good
soba without good water!
Always remember that, friends!
[GORO]
Look for yourself!
Aren't these the
most massive daikon
you've ever seen?
"Why are they so huge?"
you may ask!
Because we've
got the best manure!
[SUZUHARA]
You see? It's happening.
They're already beginning
to use the Internet
to pass them along.
The traces of their lives.
A digital archive?
Yes, exactly.
Hey, what are you
guys doing with those?
[MASA]
We're making a snow barrier.
We build barriers
around our houses now,
before the snow piles up,
to protect our windows.
Oh, wow.
It must be hard if you have
to build one for each house.
It is.
But that's why they all
work together out here.
When you live in the snow,
everyone helps each other out!
This machine is amazing!
I feel like it's taken
about fifty years off!
I've made some improvements,
but do you recognize
a Hercules Mark 3?
[YOSHINO, SHIORI laugh]
Will this get me into
the big leagues, I wonder?
[yells]
[SUZUHARA]
Thanks to all of you,
the culture and customs
of Warabiya will spread.
They'll be passed on
rather than forgotten.
I'll rescind our
declaration of withdrawal
from Chupakabura
when the timing is right.
Don't worry about that.
It's hard to believe
this was actually your goal.
You're saying you knew
it wasn't going to happen
from the start?
No, guess I still have
some small amount
of hope for us.
Hope that one day Manoyama
might change for the better.
I'll ask you again,
and be honest.
Why did you choose
to come to Manoyama?
You made the
decision to move here
on your own.
So, now that you're here,
what's the next step
on your journey?
[SANAE] To tell you the truth,
I don't know yet.
[MICHIYO coughing]
You okay, Michiyo?
Oh, sure.
It happens all the time.
I'm sorry to put you
out like this.
You're not.
The hospital's just up
ahead of us now.
[MICHIYO] I can still handle
most things these days,
but driving is too much.
[TAKAMIZAWA] Hey. Last
bus is in five minutes.
You can wait inside for it,
if you want to.
Isn't there anything
we can do?
I mean, about the
bus route problem?
Believe me, I understand
that none of this is easy.
But there's a way.
I know for a fact that
we we can figure this out.
You know? Like if everyone
would work together,
I know we could
come up with something.
I'm afraid some things just are
the way they are, Queen.
[YOSHINO]
What about the professor?
He's over eighty years old,
and he hasn't given up yet.
[sighs] The old man's
just throwing a fit.
No, he's not!
He knew they had
run out of options!
Takamizawa, do you
love this town?
Do you really care?
What?
Are you okay with all of this?
You think everything's
fine the way it is?
No, of course I don't!
I spend my life sitting
right there in that seat,
watching this town
day after day.
For over fifteen years now.
One day, the florist
goes out of business.
The next, an empty house
is crushed by snow.
Then, the elementary
school shuts down.
You really think it's possible
for a person to feel nothing?
Watching their hometown
crumble around them?
I'm sorry.
That was really presumptuous of
me. I can see I was out of line.
It's time. You coming?
There's room for you.
[YOSHINO]
I'm heading back.
[TAKAMIZAWA]
So.
Now, all the older folks know
how to use the internet, huh?
[SANAE]
Huh?
Think you could help me?
As the minister of IT and all?
You know, it's so funny.
I had something I wanted
to talk to you about, too!
I guess it's okay to stray
from the route sometimes.
[MASA] Now this here is
a Hanging Toro lantern.
You'll find, every house
here in Warabiya has one.
Look it.
Ya see what I mean?
They're to make sure
nothing out of the ordinary
is happening at our
neighbors' houses.
If the lantern's not lit,
then it means something
might have happened, so we
should go check on them.
It's a simple way
to tell if someone's safe.
I see.
File it under
"special local knowledge."
[SUZUHARA] You can't
survive out here in the cold
unless you help each other out.
If you think about it,
it's just like shoveling snow!
Yes, looking out
for others is looking out
for yourself, isn't it?
You see, Queen,
I was interested in
the thought processes
and knowledge of people
living in snowy areas.
That's why I moved here.
But wait, what happened
to the person
that used to live here?
Oh, they moved
to a senior home
in the same town
where their son lives.
The professor was about
to retire around then,
so he bought up
the entire property.
So it worked out well.
Okay! I think it's time to eat!
[SHIORI]
We're back!
Sanae, I got
the list of districts
from the Board of Tourism!
So we pick out the
addresses from the districts
one at a time, right?
Just leave it to us.
[SANAE]
Thanks! I sure will!
[MASA]
Here, have another, Sandal!
Gosh, this food is delicious!
[YOSHINO] It's a persimmon
mushroom mayonnaise risotto
topped with fava beans!
And it was made
by the queen, herself!
I read food in snowy
areas tends to be high in salt.
Well, mayonnaise is
surprisingly very low in salt!
[MASA]
Hmm?
She's being so very
considerate because she knows
I have high blood pressure.
She's simply a wonderful queen!
[YOSHINO chuckles]
That's why you've got
to take down that old loony,
Ushimatsu, and then take over
the Board of Tourism yourself!
She returns to
betray her master.
Poor Ushimatsu.
I think he's really trying,
but if you ask me,
the problem is,
he's still a pup.
If you become the permanent
Queen of Chupakabura,
we'll all happily pledge
our loyalty to you.
Kind of reminds me of Snow White
and the Seven Dwarves!
Oh, goodness, you're right!
And we've even got
a prince, haven't we?
[GROUP laughing]
No, no, you've all got it wrong.
The true prince
will arrive on a bus!
[GROUP laughing]
[YOSHINO]
And down, up!
And back, and, up!
And down--
[HIDE] Hey, there's
something down below!
[GROUP]
Huh?
It's the Manoyama
On-Demand Bus!
Take a flier!
What an incredible idea.
Yeah, so, it won't
follow a regular route.
It only runs when
someone specifically
makes a reservation!
[TAKAMIZAWA]
It's a bit of a hybrid.
Something between
a bus and a taxi.
It's a little more
expensive than a bus,
but you can get a ride
whenever you want!
And on the business side,
it's a lot more efficient
than running a big bus
that nobody rides.
Wha--?
How has no one ever
thought of this till now?
[TAKAMIZAWA] I actually
did present the idea
to my company once before.
But then, red tape.
So it didn't go through.
I bet hiring someone
to take reservations
drove up the cost.
The solution
created new problems.
That's right.
But now that these seniors
know how to use the internet,
it's opened up lots
of other options.
Then you can
open up this page
just like I showed you,
and tap the word "reservation."
After that, all you need to do
is choose the best pickup time
and your preferred location!
[MICHIYO]
Oh, it's so easy!
As of now, it'll be
limited to Manoyama,
but we've already put in
all the different addresses,
like a car GPS.
Sanae put a lot of effort
into developing the program!
[YOSHINO]
She's amazing!
We're still in
the testing phase,
but I got permission
from my company,
so go ahead and hop on board!
All right! I wanna go first!
[MAKI]
Great work!
[GORO] Hang on, Masa,
I'm getting on, too!
Your carriage has
finally arrived, my queen.
Said like the
former prince you are!
Yes, former prince, indeed!
[YOSHINO laughs]
[KIYO]
I'd like to go to Sakura Pond!
It's been a while!
That was where my husband
and I had our last date.
All right!
Wanna take a boat ride?
Ha! Can you
paddle it, old man?
[HIDE]
Didn't you throw out your back?
The on-demand bus
goes door to door,
so no walking to the bus stop.
And it's carpool,
so it's cheaper than a taxi.
It's so perfect for Manoyama!
You know,
I'm kinda blown away by how
hard you've worked on this.
I'm impressed!
I take real pride in my work.
Without this job, I wouldn't
be able to feed my family.
Self-driving cars might
take over one day.
But I'm gonna go down kicking.
[YOSHINO chuckles]
They looked like they
were having so much fun!
Being packed in like
that stokes conversation.
So, do you think
you've done it, Professor?
Is that what you
were looking for?
If I'm perfectly honest,
I didn't think it would
go this well.
Ah!
I just realized, it's high time
I gave you your course credits.
Wait, was this
some kind of test?
Oh, in that case, you
better give us all As, mister.
Well, in my opinion,
a B grade will be
more appropriate.
You tough old bugger.
[SUZUHARA]
The Kingdom of Chupakabura
did not forsake its people.
We are proud to say that
the long-held spirit
of cooperation here
is alive and well today.
We're all very grateful.
I would also like to offer
my most sincere apologies
to those who were
inconvenienced in any way
by our declaration
of withdrawal.
We hereby rescind it.
And we're proud to be part of
the Kingdom of Chupakabura.
And now, a word
from our Queen.
Huh? I'm not ready.
C'mon, nothing fancy,
just a little speech.
[YOSHINO]
Um...
I'm really sorry for all
the fuss and any trouble
that was caused.
However...
I have to admit, I love
this town even more now.
And thanks to everyone from
the Manoyama Bus Company!
Good girl.
She's so great at this.
Welp, I guess that
wraps it up, huh?
Hey, wait, what about
all the festival treasures?
We still haven't found them yet.
Almost forgot. Yeah.
There's a message
on the bulletin board.
[SANAE] It says,
"One of the festival treasures
lies in Sugita's storehouse."
Signed, Fawkes.
Who the heck is Sugita?
[music playing]
Was there any more
ice left in there?
[music continues]
[thud]
[phone rings]
Hello! This is the queen!
It was so sudden, huh?
I hope at least
he didn't suffer.
I just can't stand
the thought of that.
[KANEDA] He gave his will
to the notary ten years ago.
Left it all to the
municipal government.
I remember exactly what it says.
"I've prepared the funds to have
any and all
buildings demolished.
You can keep or reuse
them as you will.
As to what's inside, you can
do whatever you want
with all of that."
Very succinct.
He was a pretty cool guy.
He had a really nice smile.
That's an older photo.
I was able to blow it up.
[SHIORI] It still doesn't
feel real, does it?
[YOSHINO]
No.
[GORO]
Masa, I'm going to be honest.
I couldn't understand a
single bit of your eulogy!
[MASA]
It was dark.
I couldn't see the
paper properly.
What's this?
The professor's
research notebooks.
In the 20 years
since he arrived here,
he never skipped a single
day as far as I could tell.
He was doing research
the whole time he was here?
[SUZUHARA] The regions referred
to as "marginal villages"
do not simply fade
out of existence.
Through my current tests,
I have now found what I believe
to be a valuable case study.
[SANAE] So, this is what he
meant by "putting down roots."
[MASA]
Oh, that's right!
I suppose we need
to get a hold of Sugita.
Ah, of course.
Do you have his son's number?
Um, no.
Hold on, did you
just say Sugita?
[MASA]
Hm? Oh, yeah.
The guy that used
to own this place.
The message on
the bulletin board.
No way!
[YOSHINO] It's... It's one of
the festival treasures!
The Staff!
[RIRIKO] It even says
"Mizuchi Shrine" on it!
So that means it was
here all along, then.
He knew.
He knew it was here
and he didn't tell us.
[MASA laughs]
That's just like him!
Wait a minute.
Who wrote that message
on the board?
We checked so many places
and never found anything!
Maybe it was the professor.
[RIRIKO]
Signed, "Fawkes."
So he's a fox.
Just like we're the tanukis.
Huh?!
Still not going easy on us.
Nope, he's not.
How the hell are we
gonna move this thing?
Hey, I know!
I love the new bus.
It's so convenient!
Hey, now.
Just promise me you
won't abuse it, okay?
It's still in the testing phase.
[YOSHINO]
Oh, you can be so uptight!
[TAKAMIZAWA] I know you are,
but what am I?
[laughs]
[SANAE] I don't have any
ties to Manoyama, either,
just like you
when you came here.
But connections are something
you make for yourself.
I don't know what
the future holds for me,
but I wanna see what
I can do here for now.
Thank you, Professor.
Thank you.
Hey, anyway...
Isn't this thing gonna bring
us bad luck or something?
No, no worries there,
Takamizawa!
Right!
We have good intentions,
that's what matters!
[SANDAL] Does the soul have
a place to which it returns?
Tonight, I shall contemplate
this question, whiskey in hand.
[SANDAL] Next time:
"The Foggy Folklore."