[SANAE] I don't understand
why we had to come
do this at night.
[YOSHINO]
It's urgent!
We're lucky someone
posted that lead
about the festival treasure.
It'll be cool if the
Hanging Drum really is here.
Well, if it is,
then you guys should know
where they'd keep it, right?
I mean, didn't you three
go to school here?
I actually went to
the other middle school.
Yeah, so did I.
I went to this one, but I don't
remember anything about a drum.
It's been ten years
since this place shut down.
Not surprising that it's
a little creepy, huh?
[RIRIKO]
This is where he'd pop out.
The Blood-Soaked Santa.
Blood-Soaked Santa?
It's a classic urban
legend from this school.
How do you know about that?
Nope! Don't wanna
hear it! La la...
A Santa was driving
on an icy road
when he slid through a curve,
crashed, and died.
He's been wandering ever since.
[YOSHINO yelps]
C'mon, stop trying
to scare us, Riichan!
Okay, why wasn't he flying?
And why would he
come to this school?
[GROUP yelling]
[MAKI]
He's right on time.
[RIRIKO]
What is... that?
[GROUP gasps]
[YOSHINO]
It's him! Blood-Soaked Santa!
What's he carrying?
Don't tell me it's
a reindeer's corpse!
We'll all be killed.
[SHIORI] May your soul
rest in peace, sir!
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
fa-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la!
[GROUP screams]
A gorilla!
Look, it's a peeping gorilla!
[MAKI]
Would you guys calm down?
This is just my father.
[GROUP]
Huh?
Oh, I guess the
lights do work.
The school might've
been shut down,
but it wasn't abandoned.
It's still got running
water and electricity.
I assumed you must have checked
all of that stuff earlier!
[YOSHINO sighs]
I'm really sorry.
I shouldn't have called you
a gorilla, Mr. Midorikawa.
Don't worry about it;
he's an ape.
No, Maki,
because that would make
you a little ape girl
and I just can't have that!
Shiori, you really gotta work on
your mood-lightening jokes.
Thank you so much for your help
with the film shoot,
Mr. Midorikawa.
The mini-zombies.
Not at all!
The kids loved the
opportunity to do something
others don't get to do.
So, if I may ask,
what brings the Board
of Tourism here tonight?
Well, we're kind of
looking for something.
[IWAO] The Board of Education
has been getting complaints
from around the
neighborhood lately.
Kids hear these rumors
about a Blood-Soaked Santa,
so they get curious and
start poking around.
What? You really think
that's why we're here?
[IWAO]
Isn't it?
What the hell are you
doing wandering around here
at night, anyway?
Mr. Elementary School
Vice Principal!
This happens to be
my alma mater!
You think I'm happy
my beloved halls
have been turned into some
kind of haunted house?
I'm here tonight patrolling
for any shenanigans!
Um, sir?
We didn't come to snoop
around out of curiosity.
We actually got permission
to enter the school
from the Board of Education.
We're looking for
a festival treasure,
the Hanging Drum.
The one from the Mizuchi
Festival fifty years ago.
The Mizuchi Festival?
[YOSHINO] Yes, we're
planning to revive it!
Cool, right?
Okay, I get it.
Would've been better to
come in the daytime, though.
That looks less suspicious.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Let's see, I think it was here.
[IWAO]
'Kay.
[YOSHINO gasps]
It's the hanging drum!
So it really was here!
I'm glad, I'm glad.
[GROUP]
Thank you for your help!
Yeah, thanks
for all the nothin'.
What was that?!
[GROUP gasps]
Oh. I wasn't talking
about you girls, you're fine.
Hate to say it, but I
don't see how this thing
could be much use
to you in this state.
Yeah, you're prob'ly right.
[YOSHINO]
Okay, first things first:
how are we gonna move it?
We'll convince Mino
and the others
to help us out tomorrow.
Great!
Hey, Yoshi,
I've got some things to do
tomorrow, so I won't make it.
But I took care
of the other thing.
[YOSHINO]
Cool, thanks!
So, Maki, you sure are
a chip off the old block,
aren't you?
Let's be real. You and your
father have a lot in common.
Like what?
[SANAE] Why don't you take
a chance and move back home?
Your house is closer.
Staying in the dorm
doesn't make much sense.
But I would totally
miss her if she stopped
living at the dorm.
I'm trying to give her
some healthy advice!
I have no intention of moving.
So stubborn.
I just don't see
eye to eye with that guy.
[MINO]
A little more that way!
Okay. Okay.
[YAMADA]
Here we go!
[YAMADA, MINO grunt]
All right, I'm gonna
head back now.
[YOSHINO]
Okay! Thank you!
We'll definitely have
to get this thing repaired,
you know.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
I wonder how much
it's going to cost.
If it needs a new head,
it won't be cheap.
Couple hundred thousand
yen, maybe.
What? That'll screw up
our entire budget!
Well, we'll just have
to manage it somehow.
Hey, Sanae's going
to bring the car around
this way to pick us up.
Oh. Okay.
Whoa, what is this thing?
[YOSHINO] A commemorative
work for the school's
fortieth anniversary.
Apparently, all the
students and teachers
and even some of the townspeople
worked on it together.
It's beautiful.
It really is such a shame
that they're getting rid
of this place.
Getting rid of it?
It's already been settled.
It's scheduled to be demolished
the year after next.
[YOSHINO]
Really.
Yep, it's a bummer, but
maintaining it costs money, so.
[car horn beeps]
Here she is. C'mon, Yoshi!
[YOSHINO]
Oh. Coming.
[MAKI]
Is this too plain?
[SALES ASSOTIATE 19A]
Good afternoon!
Are you looking
for a gift today?
[MAKI]
Yeah. I guess.
Ta-da!
Oh, that looks really nice!
I went ahead and put the
drum in the garage for now.
Huh? What's this?
The Mizuchi Festival
Production Board.
I asked Maki to make it for us.
Nice work, Chief Handywoman!
Being an actor prepares
you for anything, huh?
The festival has been
scheduled for next April.
It's already December,
so we decided to start
by putting a board together.
Whoa, hang on!
Have you talk to
the Board of Merchants
and the Community Club?
Not yet.
We have every intention
of asking them to participate
later on, though.
In that case, I strongly
suggest that you add
the word "proposed"
in parentheses.
Proposed?
It could get a bit
thorny if it sounds like
it's already been decided.
That's a good point.
We did get into a
tiff about that before.
Thanks for the
excellent advice, Mino.
Hey, do you know
where Mr. Kadota is?
[YAMADA]
Huh?
I just had kind of an idea.
I wanna walk the same route
that the shrine float
procession used to take.
Mr. Kadota was around for it,
so I thought he might
be a good person to ask.
Yeah, he ran away, right?
Well, he was the one
who singlehandedly
forced its cancellation.
What's that?
Who's runnin' anywhere?
Oh, Mr. Kadota!
[USHIMATSU]
Gimme that!
I'll follow you to
the ends of the earth.
Wow, I think this
is the first time
I've ever thought you were cool!
Great, thanks a lot!
[YAMADA] You mind carrying
another one while you're at it?
Oh? All right, bring it on!
[YAMADA] Great, just hold
on a second, okay?
Mr. Shigaraki!
[USHIMATSU]
Bastards.
This just feels like
an updated version
of putting me in the stocks!
[SHIORI]
No worries, Mr. Kadota!
There's no one around,
so nobody will see you
in the "stocks"!
Shiori, I've totally
got déjà vu right now.
Hey, good to see you guys!
Hey, there, you too!
[TATSUO] So, you've already
put together a board, huh?
[SHIORI] Well, it's
simply being proposed.
Oh, man, that sign
is hilarious, Mr. Kadota!
Leave me alone!
I've been working on
carvings for the float.
Whenever there's
downtime at work,
that's what I'm up to.
It'll be finished by cherry
blossom season for sure!
Thank you for doing that!
[TATSUO] So how is the
float itself coming along?
Oh. Hide's been very
hard at work on it.
He's got nothing but time
on his hands, you know.
[RIRIKO] ♪ Sleep,
tonight, go and dream-- ♪
[USHIMATSU]
Out of the way!
It used to turn right here!
[SHIORI] But there's no way
this used to be the right route,
Mr. Kadota!
Listen here, Queen!
You think I'd actually
forget the way?
The shrine float can't
possibly get through here!
[door opens]
Oh, it's you guys.
Well, well. I see
you've got the old ass
out here with you, too.
Hi, Mrs. Oribe!
What's this, "The Mizuchi
Festival Production Board"?
What? Nobody told me
anything about this!
What the hell are you plotting?
Shut up!
It's none of your business, hag!
Just proposed, see? Proposed!
Nothing at all has been
set in stone yet!
We'll come by soon
to discuss it with you,
if that would be all right!
Yeah, well, whatever.
Regardless, all that matters
is whether or not he's serious.
Meaning?
You were the one
who destroyed the festival
to begin with.
So you had better
see this thing through!
That's what I'm doing right now!
Oh, really?
You actually think
that's what you're doing?
[USHIMATSU] Shut it, you
old hag! Who do you--
[SHIORI] This is where
they'd load the shrine float
onto the boat and continue
the procession on water,
isn't that right?
Yep, that's right.
All that's left is the singing
and dancing after that.
What exactly was
the festival originally for?
I dunno.
I was just a little
punk back then.
I'm not so sure anyone
else thought too deeply
about the meaning, either.
It was just something
they did out of habit.
So at some point,
they forgot the reason
and they were just
going through the motions
more than anything else.
Simply reviving the festival
isn't going to be enough.
We need to think of
something new and exciting.
Something that'll inspire
the people of Manoyama.
[USHIMATSU] That's the
direction the float used to go.
There should be an
old shrine over there.
Wanna check it out?
Sure!
Honestly, I was a little
worried about all of this.
[USHIMATSU]
All of what?
I was mainly worried that
you wouldn't wanna help us!
That would've totally sucked!
Well, it's true that I wouldn't
have started this myself,
even with a gun to my head.
In my own way,
I still do feel responsible
for what happened.
That's why I've constantly
tried to do things
I thought would
help the town out.
Tried like a madman.
[YOSHINO]
I get that.
[USHIMATSU] Still, I know I've
got to address the core issue
and start over from there.
It's about time.
And now, all thanks to you,
I've got no choice
but to face it.
You really are a troublemaker.
[chuckles]
Thank you, Mr. Kadota.
[SANAE]
Oden's late tonight.
I know, I've been
wondering where she went.
Hey, maybe she went on a date!
[YOSHINO chuckles]
[MAKI]
I told you, I'm going back.
[KOSUKE]
Come on, Maki!
I only came by here to
drop off a present for Mom.
[KOSUKE]
You're already here, though.
Why don't you stay for dinner?
[MAKI] I don't want to!
He's here, isn't he?
Nope, he's got a late meeting.
That means you're staying.
--[MAKI] Wait--
--[KOSUKE] Come on!
Mom! Maki's here for dinner!
[SUMIKO]
How lovely!
And it's very warm, too.
Thank you, Maki.
Sure.
[SUMIKO]
How many years has it been?
You've lost weight, haven't you?
Hmm? I don't know.
[SUMIKO]
You little ingrate.
Come on now, Mom.
I understand it's tough
for you to see your dad,
but I wish you would
come to see me.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
[SUMIKO] You know,
he's not even that upset
about you quitting college.
Not anymore.
Really? You think?
[SUMIKO] Yeah!
Anyway, it's time for dinner!
[IWAO]
♪ Today is Sumiko's birthday! ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Sumiko! ♪
[gasps]
[CAT meows]
Welcome home, dear!
Why is it oden?
[SUMIKO] I swear, I didn't
know you were coming!
You better eat
before Dad drains it all.
Kosuke!
Acknowledging him
makes it worse.
[IWAO] If you don't
like it, don't eat it.
All right, I'm leaving now.
[IWAO]
You haven't been excused yet!
Make up your mind!
Why did you drop out of
college before you'd even
talked to us about it one time?
Uh... He seems
pretty upset to me.
Well...
[IWAO] And what happened to
your acting career, anyway?
This is great daikon!
Well, it can't be worse
than rotten tomatoes.
--Yeah...
--Don't you get mad at him!
Would you prefer a
cicada or two with that?
No, I wouldn't, thanks!
What were you doing
checking late-night TV
for me, anyway?
I just happened
to be watching it,
and you showed up
out outta the blue!
It wasn't even
broadcast in Manoyama!
So, you just dropped out of
college to eat cicadas, did you?
As a matter of fact,
I never ate cicadas!
Stop this! Both of you!
I'm the star of the
show tonight, right?
--[IWAO] Yes, dear.
--[MAKI] Yes, ma'am.
[MAKI] Sorry. It always
ends up like this.
I don't mind, though.
It keeps things lively, right?
I really wish you'd
move back in.
I know it doesn't seem like it,
but Dad cares about you.
He's watched every single
show you've had a part in.
[MAKI]
Oh, god.
That just makes it harder
to come back, honestly.
Hey Maki, wait a sec!
I forgot to tell you,
you received a letter
in the mail the other day.
[MAKI]
Yeah?
From Tokyo.
What? No way.
Director Ryotaro Kurose.
The Kurose?
Yeah.
I didn't think there was
any way I'd actually get in.
So if he likes your audition,
you'll for real be in
one of his movies?
When's the date?
Whoa, that's in two days!
Yeah. I'm not going.
I only submitted because
my friend asked me to.
I've got a steady
job here, anyway.
What are you saying Maki?
This is your chance!
You've always wanted
this opportunity!
I left that and came
back to Manoyama.
That's my answer.
[YOSHINO] Shut-down schools
end up getting repurposed
a lot, don't they?
They've helped rural revival
efforts, too, sometimes.
Huh.
Why do you think they aren't
using the one in Manoyama?
--[door opens]
--Hey, you're back!
It's late. Have you had dinner?
Sorry, yeah,
I ended up eating out.
What're you guys doing?
We've been researching
about the middle school.
We were just thinking
that it's a waste
not to use such
a wonderful building!
Whoa, some schools
are even letting
private companies
use them for free!
How about using it
as a hotel for the festival?
Then, visitors wouldn't
have to camp out
like they did for
the Founding Festival.
Using it for lodging
would create
an awful lot of hurdles, though.
It's got to be renovated, and
there'll be a ton of paperwork.
Then we'll turn it into
Chupakabura Academy!
Wait, an academy?
It was shut down because there
weren't enough students here!
I still think it's a good idea.
The Royal Chupakabura Academy!
I like your style, Queen.
G'night.
[YOSHINO]
You dropped something.
Marvin... Productions?
--What's this?
--[MAKI] It's nothing.
Work I never got paid for.
I think I have an idea.
[SHIORI] A hot lunch party?
I love that!
And there are cases
where it helped rural
revival efforts, too!
Well, first we've gotta
get people thinking
about the school itself.
Agreed. I feel like we should
discuss it with people
that went there.
Know of anyone?
I did. Gimme a look!
Aww. Man, If I didn't have
to work, I'd love to go.
I'd be happy to talk to the
Community Club for you.
Great! Thanks!
Why the heck would
anyone want to go eat
gross hot lunch in
a haunted school?
Come on, Erika!
You don't know if
it's gross or not!
Yeah, I do!
You'd get more people if it was
a haunted house, you know.
That's good stuff.
It's not gross!
You just hate it because
you're still in school,
so you have no choice
but to eat it.
When you get older,
you'll find you kinda
miss it, like we do.
Hot dog buns.
Or that kinda spiceless curry!
[sighs]
I'm so glad you're here.
Uh, welcome. Hi.
What is it?
It's just...
I have something I want to
tell you guys, about Maki.
[MAKI] It's not every day
you to invite me over, huh?
What's up? You good?
[RIRIKO] I wanted to
upload the Dragon Song
on the Manoyama Channel
so lots of people
could see it whenever
they wanted to.
--Oh, nice!
--But lately...
I'm starting to feel
like my singing is off.
You're the only one
I can go to for advice,
since you're an actor and all.
I see.
Okay.
So should I start with
more or less vibrato?
[MAKI]
No, that's not what it's about.
It's the same thing with acting.
It's not really about whether
you're good or bad,
but whether you're
able to connect.
It's about being honest.
Audiences just wanna
feel something.
Lead them there by
expressing your feelings.
'Kay. I'll try.
♪ Sleep tonight, go and dream ♪
♪ Feel the comfort of our song ♪
♪ A piece missing alone ♪
♪ Frightened and seeking home ♪
♪ Please forgive us for all
we should have known ♪
[MAKI humming]
--[BOY 19A] Come on! Come on!
--[BOY 19B] Wait for me!
They tried, but they couldn't
pull up the big kabu.
So the dog decided to come
over and help them out!
--[barking]
--[CHILDREN laughing]
[SANDAL] Unfortunately,
the kabu didn't budge one bit.
And the poor little dog's
dentures came loose!
--[SANDAL howling]
--[CHILDREN laughing]
[SANDAL] Then, wouldn't you
know, the cat came to help!
Meow! But the kabu still
wouldn't budge an inch!
[CHILDREN]
Aww!
[SANDAL] Then, tragically,
the cat's favorite nail polish
came off!
--[SANDAL meowing]
--[CHILDREN laughing]
[IWAO] I had a meeting with
the Board of Education.
A paper play? Haven't seen
one of those in a while.
Who makes a face like that
when they're watching
a paper play?
I was born this way.
No, you weren't.
You smiled a lot
when you were little.
You know, you should
really stick with acting.
[MAKI] But... I can't
make a living that way.
I took a lot of odd
jobs just to survive.
After a while,
I wasn't sure why I ever went
to Tokyo in the first place.
[IWAO] Who said it had
to make you a living?
Is it really that
hard for you, Maki?
Continuing to love
the things you love?
[MAKI]
Huh?
[IWAO] You smiled a lot,
when you were little.
You did.
Hey, guys. I'm home!
Kosuke told us about the letter.
The audition is tomorrow, right?
Aren't you going?
My goal right now is to
make the festival a success,
as Chief Handywoman for
the Kingdom of Chupakabura.
I don't think it's the
right time for an audition.
It is the right time!
The opportunity is
right in front of you!
If you don't try,
you're always gonna regret it!
I'm doing the best
I can as Queen,
and I think the work
is very worthwhile.
I'm glad I'm here.
But after that, next year,
I don't know what to do.
I don't have a long term dream.
I haven't found anything yet.
You've known what
you've wanted for yourself
ever since you were little!
That alone is amazing!
[SANAE]
Let's get to the station.
You should just be able to
make it by the end of the day.
Maki, go!
[train horn blares]
[SANDAL] Santa Claus used
to come visit our house
when I was little,
but when we started using
those little roach motels,
he stopped showing up.
Next time: "The Phoenix
in the Holy Night."