[USHIMATSU] I think we may be
facing the end of Manoyama.
[YOSHINO]
What?
[USHIMATSU] I've been
hearing rumors for a while,
but plans are apparently
moving forward, now.
We'll be absorbed into Tomikura.
[gasps]
We'll be what?
As head of Manoyama's
Board of Tourism.
I've been secretly invited to
serve on the Absorption Council.
[YOSHINO sighs]
Absorption.
[MAKI] I always figured it
was only a matter of time
before something
like that happened.
Surely, it's not happening
right away though, right?
Well, normally,
they set up a council
and then slowly start
to readjust things
while getting residents'
opinions along the way.
It can take up to two years.
So, in two years,
Manoyama might be gone.
It might be gone in name,
but it's not going to disappear!
Yeah, the district
names might stay,
but oftentimes, a city gets
renamed something weird
after being absorbed.
As far as I can tell
from these examples,
it doesn't seem like
all that bad of a thing
to happen to a town.
But, I'm not ready
to say goodbye
to the Manoyama of my childhood.
It's incredibly sad.
That's why what we do
now is so important!
We have to work hard.
We'll keep Manoyaman
culture alive!
That should be our goal
while we're planning
the Mizuchi Festival!
We'll fill it with things
Manoyamans hold dear,
and all they want
to keep holding dear.
Yeah, you're right.
Sitting here worrying
isn't going to help.
[YOSHINO]
Nope!
We need to focus our
efforts on making sure
the Mizuchi Festival
is a great success!
[YOSHINO]
Nice!
We can start hanging
them up all over town!
[YAMADA]
Hey, the happi have arrived!
Wow!
They're so cute!
Go on, try one on, Yoshi!
Sure!
Look at this!
Too bad we only have enough
for council members
and people carrying the float.
You know what would be awesome?
If we could get enough happi
for all the different people
that are helping out.
I'm afraid that's just
not possible on our budget.
Lemme dream, huh?
Good morning, Mr. Kadota!
[USHIMATSU]
Hey.
Today, let the festival
make you forget
all about the absorption!
And if you can't forget,
we'll expand our territory,
and call ourselves
Chupakabura City.
Or, maybe we won't
attempt any of that at all.
Hmph! You're a fool.
Wow, kinda looks like
all this talk about absorption
has been quite
a shock for the boss.
Is it bad that I'm
hoping it might make him
calm down a bit, though?
In his youth he was apparently
always known as the young fool.
He's already lost
the young part,
so, is he really going to
lose the foolish part next?
Isn't that good?
I don't know.
I think it's kind
of sad, to be honest.
My dear queen,
you're adopting his crazy.
[USHIMATSU]
Hey, I know her!
I know this creature!
This is the dragon girl
and she's a menace!
[SHIBUKAWA]
What's so menacing about her?
Well, boy, if she's
actually a dragon,
then she's got to be
a menace, period!
Dragons are extremely
intelligent creatures, though.
If we decide to befriend her
and receive her knowledge,
she could help the
village tremendously.
What on earth
are you talking about?
Befriending a dragon is
totally absurd, Elder!
[TAIRA]
People of the village!
Which are you going to believe?
The words of the Elder
or those of the Chief?
Did they come to you, too?
Are you on the council?
Yes, they contacted
me yesterday.
I've been wondering what
would be the best thing
for the future of the town.
What are you so upset about?
Manoyama has survived
as long as it has
by getting knowledge
from outside,
and then, consistently
changing with it.
We had completely forgotten
that important part of our past,
but the queen, an outsider,
has thankfully reminded us.
Yes, I am fully
aware of all of that.
Then, see?
There's nothing to worry about.
So, before we start
squabbling over absorption,
there's one thing
that we should do.
We have to commit to
making completely certain
that future generations
don't forget, the way we did.
[USHIMATSU]
Hmm...
[ANGELICA]
Welp, there we go!
Hey, by the way, I heard
about the absorption thing.
Yeah, I guess the time
has finally come, huh?
Getting absorbed by
Tomikura will be totally boring.
We should join
Harajuku, instead!
I'm not sure
that's how it works.
I like absorbent things.
It helps a lot if they
happen to be quilted, too.
We're not a paper towel, though.
So, are all you guys
completely against this?
Well, yeah, I'd rather
not get absorbed, right?
I don't know, Manoyama's
budget is pretty tight,
so if we get absorbed
by Tomikura,
it'll probably end up improving
quite a few things around here.
We'll be the minority though,
so it will be hard to
get them to listen to us.
And then, there's a good chance
our culture and traditions
will be discarded and forgotten.
Even if we revive the festival,
you think it won't be enough
to pass those things down?
Look, remember, what's important
is how strongly everyone feels
about keeping the
Mizuchi festival alive.
That's a good thing.
It'll be just fine.
I'm sure!
Yes!
We'll make it so
awesome that everyone
will be sure to love it!
And, we can always have
a local referendum, too.
In the end, the
responsibility's all up to us.
[door opens]
[ANGELICA]
Welcome, sir!
[YOSHINO]
Amamiya?
It's good to see you again.
Been a long time since
the Founding Festival.
Anyhow, I heard you
might be here, so...
I'm glad you found me.
What's going on?
Well I...
Look, honestly,
there's something
I wanted share with you.
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
[MAKI]
Huh?!
What do you mean,
"casting change"?
They want you to put
a local idol in the play.
Some star from
Northern Living Television.
[MAKI]
What the hell?
The idols are all in the variety
show that Kume hosts, too.
They say that their
idol would, of course,
play the role of
the dragon girl,
and they also want her
to take Riichan's place
in singing the dragon song.
Wha?
Kind of pushy.
He's got the
prime-time live slot,
and he's willing
to let us use up all of it
for a live broadcast
of the Mizuchi Festival.
Man, I don't know,
I mean, even if he is--
Uh! No worries!
Of course we aren't
going to agree to that.
Right.
That's why Amamiya came
to give us a heads up.
Kume is going to be stopping
by with a proposal for you.
Think very carefully
about what it would mean
for Manoyama, before you reply.
"Honestly"? He's on our side?
He apologized for what happened
with "Moving Mountains."
Kume edited it to
maximize their ratings,
and Amamiya couldn't
very well go against him.
Apparently, it was not
what Amamiya wanted.
I think it'll just be a repeat
of the Founding Festival.
I feel like we should
definitely refuse.
Still...
[MAKI]
A TV broadcast.
Considering how many people
would learn about the festival,
turning him down outright might
be a little foolish on our part.
[YOSHINO] We all really
put our heads together
to come up with
these compromises.
She can take
the role of a villager,
or she can not
participate in the play,
but instead come to
the festival to do a report
on the food there.
[USHIMATSU]
I've got a question.
Huh?
Are these proposals based
on what you'd actually like
to have happen with this thing?
You don't think you'll
regret it later?
Don't think so. I don't know.
[YAMADA] Northern Living
Television is here!
[USHIMATSU]
Hmm?
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
[KUME]
Well, what do you think?
They're all pretty cute,
aren't they?
We're really looking forward
to working with
you again, Mr. Kadota!
Ah! Here's a thought!
After the Mizuchi Festival,
maybe you could also
consider one of them
to be the next
Queen of Manoyama!
Listen, we really appreciate
you bringing this to us,
but we were hoping
you'd take a look
at our suggestions now.
Suggestions?
Well, yeah. So, for example--
We won't negotiate!
Sorry, but we're through here.
We can't possibly
accept this proposal.
Wait, hang on now!
What seems to be
the problem, Mr. Kadota?
Having the festival
broadcast live isn't exactly
a bad deal for Manoyama!
I've heard there
are talks of Tomikura
absorbing Manoyama, too.
It's all the more reason
to really put this festival
on display, and try to--
We're trying to revive
a traditional festival!
It's imperative that we be
able to do things our way!
[KUME]
Of course, but--
This festival
belongs to Manoyama!
We're not going
to let you mess with it!
Uh...
[MINO]
Jeez, boss!
Did you have to yell
at him like that?
[YAMADA] I know we can't accept
all of the proposal, as-is,
but I think it would have
been better to negotiate a bit
and have the chance
to show off our town on--
Oh, shut up!
The word "negotiate"
has never been
a part of my vocabulary!
What? What? What's so funny?
Sorry.
Nothing, really, just thinking
you're a fool, that's all.
You're certainly
one to talk, Queen.
Oh, stop.
You just happened
to remind me of it.
I hope, when I'm older,
I'll still be as much of
a young fool as you are!
So, now, the Shrine
Float is seaworthy!
On the night of
the Mizuchi Festival,
this float will make
its way around the city,
and then return to Sakura Pond!
[RIRIKO]
Cut. Okay.
People of Manoyama,
get ready for the
Mizuchi Festival revival!
The countdown is
a really good idea, I think.
[SANAE] And we'll upload
new content daily, too,
so it stays fresh!
Look, lots of people are already
posting clips of their own!
This is so fun!
My car is ready to go!
It's decked out
in festival mode.
[RIRIKO] Masa's bragging
about his big kabura again.
Looks like he's
counting down, too.
[SANAE] Hey, did Kosuke figure
out where he's going to college?
A music college in Tomikura,
majoring in percussion.
Wow!
He's really going to be
a professional taiko player!
[YOSHINO] This float will
make its way around the city,
and then return to Sakura Pond!
[SANAE] We don't need to rely
on Northern Living Television!
We've got the Manoyama Channel!
[SHIORI laughs]
This is a festival for
Manoyamans, after all!
[YOSHINO]
That's right!
It's far more important
to try to get people excited
inside the city, rather than
focusing on people outside!
[buzzing]
Momonga Agency?
This is Yoshino!
Good to hear from you!
Hold on just a sec.
[MAKI]
Huh?
[SANAE] Come on,
we can't let them outdo us!
We've got to think up
something really innovative
and unique that we can post!
Oh, what's this?
[roars]
[screams]
Oh no, the Chupakabura!
It's a little
embarrassing now, isn't it?
Right? I can't even
believe we made this thing.
I didn't know that page existed.
Do you think Yoshino
has grown up a little bit,
compared to back then?
Yeah, I think so, for sure.
Huh? Look at this.
Oh!
Come to think of it,
we did discuss that.
That's right!
You guys, I've got an idea!
Come on, you can't possibly
eat ten servings of katsudon!
[CHALLENGER]
I can! I can eat 11!
Here you go, tea is served.
Oh! Is this the program
that you shooed away?
[USHIMATSU]
Hmph!
[KINU chuckles]
Are you regretting it now?
I don't regret it at all.
But I can't help wondering if
there might not be something
that I could do for
Manoyama on my own.
Something that only I could do.
[MINO]
Yes!
Of course, we'll happily
accept your donation!
Thank you so much!
Would you like us
to email those forms,
or fax them to you?
[MINO]
Uh... You don't have either?
[YAMADA]
Okay, thank you for calling!
[YOSHINO] Umm, I'd be happy to
go and deliver those directly.
Oh, thank you. Yes, please!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Man, we're getting more
and more individual donations!
I know!
The whole town is
really coming together,
all for the sake
of the festival!
[OBASAN] Thank you for
coming out here like this!
[YOSHINO]
Oh, not at all!
Thank you for your help!
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
Kumano? Sayuri?
What are you guys doing?
Are you scouting out
a rival restaurant?
Well, not exactly.
I guess I've been inspired.
I might open a new location
in the shopping district.
Its specialty would
be French toast!
Oh!
[SANAE] Running off to France,
opening restaurants.
Kumano is quite the go-getter!
Cool, huh?
They found a cafe that
closed up shop last year.
The owner said he'd let
Kumano rent the space!
Hello there!
I thought you guys might
like some croquettes!
Oh, those croquettes
from the butcher!
--[TAEI] Thank you!
--[KOTOMI] Oh yummy, Thank you!
After all this, now it seems
like the shopping district
is full of energy.
It certainly is.
Maybe I'll open an office
in the shopping district
after the festival.
[MAKI]
What'll you do, Queen?
Uh. What do you mean?
You got a call from your
agency earlier, didn't you?
Ah... Yeah. They called
about the contract ending.
Will you go back to Tokyo?
Huh?! Oh, Yoshi, you're not
gonna stay in Manoyama?
I'm still thinking it over.
I was considering moving
back to my hometown, too.
So, does that
mean you gave up
on finding a "not normal"
job in Tokyo?
[YOSHINO]
Yeah.
Even if I got a job like that,
I'm sure it would seem
normal after a while.
I think anything would.
And even in a totally normal
job, you find inspiration.
I know in Tokyo
there's always a lot going on,
but I don't think inspiration
always has to come
from the outside.
It's within yourself.
So, you can really
find it wherever you are.
That's what I've learned from
coming here and experiencing
so many different
things with all of you.
Whatever your job is,
if you invest yourself,
you can find inspiration in it,
and mine it for
all that it's worth.
That's what I believe now.
That's so cool.
Agreed, well said.
You have really
grown a lot, girl.
You know what?
You've inspired me in
so many ways this year.
You, too.
I only learned this
stuff because of you.
You've made me better.
Thank you.
So, at the very end,
the float will travel
across the water and
return the shine here.
[DOKU]
Yep, that's why
we're scrubbing away
50-year-old grime.
I de-grime in a bath for 50
minutes three times a day.
Someone's obsessed
with cleanliness, isn't he?
[laughs]
What is this?
[YOSHINO]
What? What?
There are names carved here.
Probably the names
of the people involved
with Sakura Pond's construction.
It's okay, Leave this to me.
This shrine was
moved to this spot
when they were working
on the reservoir
and making Sakura Pond,
isn't that right?
Yeah.
All of that happened well
before I was even born.
They apparently called
in a foreign civil engineer
for the designing of the pond.
I've finally found it.
Proof of their life here.
These are my roots.
Now that you mention it,
didn't you say your name was...
He's Alexandre Sena
Davis Celibidache.
My middle names are
from my great grandmother
and my great grandfather.
They met in Manoyama,
and fell in love at Sakura Pond.
So, your ancestors
actually made Sakura Pond!
That's amazing!
And it's super romantic, too!
I bet they went to the
festival together, huh?
They must have.
What a crazy
find this is for me.
And now I'll go to the
festival, just like they did.
Two days left until
the Mizuchi Festival!
Aaah! You little thief!
[SANAE]
Yep. Ridiculous as always.
But look!
Now everything is
finally coming together.
The cherry blossoms
are looking good.
At this rate,
they're going to be in
full bloom for the festival!
Yoshino! Can you give me a hand?
What's up?
Could you get in there
and then hold the doors
from the inside for me?
[YOSHINO]
Got it!
Wow, pretty realistic in here!
Huh?
Oooo, it's dark.
I can't see anything!
Where the heck are the doors?
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
Maki? You there? Hello?
They're locked!
What's going on out there?
[cheering]
[SHIORI]
Ready, and...
[ALL]
Happy birthday to our queen!
Oh, wow.
You guys remembered the day.
We very nearly forgot
with all the festival prep.
Oh! The happis!
Yeah, but to be clear,
we weren't trying to wish
you a "happi" birthday.
Remember what
you said the other day?
How you thought it'd be
nice if we had a happi
for everybody helping
out with the festival?
Turns out, everyone
agreed with you.
So we went out
and got the same ones.
Oh, you guys.
[YOSHINO]
Wow.
A Japanese-style cake?
That's right.
A Western treat, crafted
by a Japanese confectioner.
So, it's not normal.
It's a special cake.
All right, I think it's time
for her to blow out the candles.
Come on, do it, Yoshi!
[YOSHINO]
Mm.
Okay.
Thank you, everyone!
Happy birthday!
[SHIORI]
[YOSHINO]
Thanks for being you!
Now, let's go, and make
this festival the best, ever!
[YOSHINO]
Good morning, everyone!
I want you to know,
it's your hard work
and commitment that
have made all this possible!
The Mizuchi Festival is back!
Let's all enjoy it and
have a great time today!
[MEN] Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
Wasshoi! Wasshoi! Wasshoi!
[USHIMATSU]
This festival. This town.
I can't let them disappear.
[USHIMATSU]
Oh! Squeaky-clean now, huh?
Hmm? What's with this rock?
The names of the
people that originally
created Sakura Pond
are carved there.
Including Sandal's
great grandmother
and great grandfather, too!
[USHIMATSU]
Hmm...
We might be able to use this!
Use it for what?
[USHIMATSU] We can make
sister cities of Manoyama
and Sandal's hometown!
You're right.
"The two hometowns of a
couple who met here long ago."
I can't think of a
more perfect set up
for sister cities, can you?
No, and if Manoyama
had a sister city,
it might just be enough
to give us some leverage
in the absorption.
[MINO] What kind of leverage
are we talking about here?
I don't know!
But anything's gotta be better
than sitting here
twiddling our thumbs.
Sandal, I'm gonna need
you to put me in touch
with your town's mayor!
I'm not actually
friends with the mayor.
But we do follow each
other on social media.
Oh, wow, what a coincidence!
Mayor Naumann
happens to be in the middle
of a private trip right now.
"Seeing cherry
blossoms in Japan."
In Kanazawa.
Has he posted
anything from there?
"The cherry blossoms at
Kenroku-en have already fallen."
Yes, this is our chance!
He's gotta see Sakura
Pond's cherry blossoms
and the Festival!
And, while they're at it,
we'll discuss
becoming sister cities!
Have you lost your mind?
I'm driving straight
to Kanazawa!
Wha?
Mr. Kadota?
[YOSHINO]
What! He left for Kanazawa?
[CHITOSE] Can't that idiot bring
himself to act like an adult,
just this once?
[DOKU]
Same old Ushimatsu.
The idiot who once destroyed the
festival and made it disappear
is now the guy tryin'
to keep it alive.
He swore that he would
definitely be back in time
for the dragon play, though.
Do you girls trust him?
You just never know.
It could be like 50 years ago.
It's okay!
I believe we can trust him!
[SANDAL]
It was a long, long trip,
but we're finally coming
to the end of the journey.
Thank you, Manoyama
and Chupakabura.
And thank you, five heroes.
Next: "The Kingdom
of Cherry Blossoms."