Oh, hey, I'm sorry!
I totally thought you guys
were only coming to watch today.
[YOSHINO] Mm-mm. It's okay.
We didn't tell you.
Our sun protection efforts
were all for naught, then.
[SANAE] Aw, I was looking
forward to getting down in it.
I guess I didn't realize
agriculture was automated.
[MAKI]
Why are you such a grandma?
What are you wearing?
[SANAE] I don't wanna get
bitten up by bugs, all right!
I'm sure most people assume
agriculture involves
heavy labor, but this is
what it's actually like.
Thanks so much for coming out
to see us, everyone.
Sure!
And since we're here,
is there anything
we can do to help you out today?
[TAKAYUKI]
Yeah!
We could have you guys cut
the corners of the field!
--[YOSHINO] 'Kay!
--[MAKI] Cool!
[RIRIKO]
Mission accepted.
Woah. Wait a minute,
if your mom and dad are both
right here, then, who's driving?
Oh, look at that.
Are they shooting another movie?
No, these are my
friends from work!
It's Yoshi, the Queen,
and her ministers!
Ah. The ones you
always talk about!
It's great to finally meet after
hearing so much about you!
I'm the big sis, Sayuri!
That's so cool!
So, you're actually
a nurse, then, Sayuri?
You know the big
general hospital
the next town over?
She's in pediatrics.
Wow! That must keep
you pretty busy.
Yeah, my schedule's
always changing
and it's pretty crazy.
But I love working
with children!
Come on, you need to eat up!
We've got to get some color
back into those cheeks!
Thanks, there never was any.
Your family's food
is so yummy, Shiori!
You gotta brother I could marry?
I know, right?
I don't really get it.
I mean, these are just
regular somen noodles!
[SANAE]
It's unique, though!
You put menma on it!
Huh? Who doesn't put
menma on somen ?
Don't laugh, she says silly
things like that sometimes.
Attack of the airheaded sisters.
[SHIORI]
Hey, I'm not an airhead!
My hand's up.
Queen, may I speak?
What is it, dear Minister of IT?
Just a thought.
Why don't we have Shiori
lead the C-Rank Gourmet?
[MAKI]
Seconded.
[gasps] No way, I can't do that!
I can't be the
leader of anything!
Wait, what is C-rank Gourmet?
We're creating an exclusive,
signature dish for the
kingdom of Chupakabura!
We're hoping people will travel
to Manoyama just to eat it!
That's a fun project!
We had something
like that in the town
about ten years back, didn't we?
The, uh, Manoyama Burger?
That's it.
Oh, you mean
that weird hamburger
with the pickled
Kabura on it, right?
It was a flop-and-
a-half, of course.
Who came up with
that idea, anyway?
Yeah, I'm pretty
sure we know who.
We know exactly who.
Yes, this is just
what I ordered.
You did a great job.
Thanks, I'm glad
you're pleased, sir.
[MINO]
Chupakabura Manju Deluxe?
[USHIMATSU] Yeah, I decided
I would update our manju
for the Queen's new
C-Rank Gourmet project.
I can't believe you went and did
something like that again.
The Board of Merchants
isn't gonna like it.
Well, they can't get mad
if it increases tourism.
Plus, I got it
done on the cheap!
First, Chef Kouzuki!
Indeed!
[YOSHINO]
What is that, chef?
I call it "A Cup
of Flying Noodles."
The plating portrays
a delightful encounter
between ramen and chicken wings!
So it's supermarket
chicken wings
in a cup of instant ramen.
Please step down, chef.
Fair.
[YOSHINO]
And, next!
Chef Oribe! Explain your dish.
It's a Garden
Caterpillar Pastry.
We should avoid making
bug-themed food if we can.
Plus, it looks like it has
cream coming out of its butt.
That's what I like about it.
[YOSHINO] Please step down.
Next, Chef Midorikawa!
I kinda went for
quantity over quality.
It's the Mega Tempura Sandwich.
That's something a student
might come up with.
It's too thrown-together.
Hold on. You're one
to talk, Ms. Queen.
What the hell is that?
[YOSHINO] Croquette Peanut
Butter Curry Yakisoba!
Cropeacur Yakisoba,
for short! It's really good!
[MAKI]
It's a big brown pile!
[SANAE] I guess we can't just
throw things together, huh?
That's true.
More importantly,
none of your dishes
have anything to
do with Manoyama.
And where's the dish you
made, Chef Shinomiya?
Chicken with ankake
sauce and kabura !
[ALL]
Boring.
Really? But I don't think so.
[SANAE] Okay, but seriously,
this stuff is pretty good.
Look, the "C" in C-Rank Gourmet
stands for "champion."
It's got to have real
impact if it's gonna be
Manoyama's special dish!
Well, why don't we bring
some of the local restaurants
in on the project?
I think we're all
a little too biased
to be working on it alone.
That's a good idea.
[SANAE] I still think you
should head this up, Shiori.
Yeah, if we leave it
up to the Queen,
we'll probably end up
with food poisoning.
I'm right here!
I prefer staying out
of the spotlight
and supporting other people.
I have no desire to be out
in front, taking the lead.
Neither do I.
Scary right?
The thought of
taking responsibility
if everything fails
is so overwhelming.
Thanks for your
faith in the project.
So, you're finally back home?
[CHIKAKO] It's been a while
since the whole family
went out to eat together.
Isn't this place expensive?
Don't worry about it,
I just got my summer bonus.
I want everyone to order
whatever they want!
It's pretty surreal
to hear those words
coming out of my
firstborn's mouth!
[SAYURI] Well, it isn't
exactly The Last Supper,
but I wanted to go
somewhere with everyone
before I moved out.
[sobs]
Come on, honey.
The girls have to
grow up sometime!
I bet work would be kinda tough
if you didn't live
close to the hospital.
Hey, now.
Don't you start saying
you're going to miss me
or I'm gonna lose it.
[SHIORI]
Of course I will!
But, for now, let's just enjoy
a delicious meal together!
Which one of these is snails?
If you want snails,
there are plenty outside.
And they're free.
[YOSHINO] Hm, I don't know,
can you make the date
jump out a bit more? So it
stands out as you go past?
Yeah, no prob.
Burning the midnight
oil, are we?
Yep, there's a lot
riding on this plan.
But I know we can pull it off.
We'll attract tons of tourists
and make the merchants happy!
[CHITOSE sighs]
What a long day.
Welcome home, Grandma.
Well, well, this is
a rare sight!
Are you actually making
us some dinner?
That's very kind of you, Ririko.
[RIRIKO]
You're back late.
[CHITOSE] I'm getting ready for
the annual summer festival.
It's usually very profitable
for the Board of Merchants.
We've gotta get our
product out there, too.
[CHITOSE]
Let me try a little.
How 'bout we order
some take-out?
[RIRIKO]
Mm-hm.
[TAKAYUKI] How're things on
the dating front, Shiori?
Aren't there any
nice guys at work?
[SHIORI]
Are you kidding? No way!
I like the idea of marrying
a civil servant, though,
and he could also help us out
in the fields on his days off!
Not to mention, he's stylish
and good-looking, right?
Well, if he was, I
certainly wouldn't complain!
Good thing you haven't set
your standards too high.
Oh, sure, there are tons
of guys like that around!
[ALL laugh]
You're a good girl, Shiori.
[NAKAYAMA]
Here you are.
Roast boar with balsamic
sauce and myoga ginger.
Delicious!
And the meat is so tender!
That glass shrimp and
chilled kabura potage
was incredibly tasty, too!
This would be great
for the C-rank Gourmet!
Cool idea!
I imagine this place uses lots
of local ingredients, right?
Yes!
In this dish, both the
boar and the ginger
are locally sourced.
Oh, my gosh,
it could really work.
[KUMANO]
My apologies!
This asparagus was supposed
to go along with that dish!
Uh, pardon me,
I'm the chef, Kumano.
[GANJURO] So you're the
one running this place?
Not bad for a young kid!
Oh, yes, it's my place now,
thank you very much.
Hey, long time, no see, Kumano.
[gasps] Shinomiya?
You guys friends?
We were classmates
in high school.
You went off to train in France
right after we graduated, yeah?
That's right!
This used to be a
noodle shop, didn't it?
Yes, this is my family's.
My father's unfortunately
not in good health,
so he let me come
and take over here.
I had no idea you
were back home now.
I'm a little late
on this, but congrats!
Thanks a lot.
[SAYURI]
Your dream came true, huh?
Yeah.
[CHIYO] Mr. Kumano,
are you a single gentleman?
[KUMANO]
Hm? Oh, uh, yes, I am.
We have two granddaughters!
Take your pick! Really!
Granny, stop!
What the heck are
you talking about?
Uh...
You're kind.
But I'm afraid they
would be wasted on me.
I don't know about that.
[yelps]
Seriously, how am I
supposed to catch a fish
with my bare hands?
Shiori said it's very
important that we use
ingredients that are in season!
I never said we had to get them
straight from the river!
[yelps]
And I used to work
at an eel restaurant.
There's a bear right over there.
--Huh?!
--[SHIORI] What?
Mister Kumano?
[gasps]
This is so good!
Isn't it though?
Just a bit of salt and a big
ol' bite. It really is the best!
It's funny to hear that
coming from a French chef!
I never would've imagined
there were so many
cool things about Manoyama!
[KUMANO]
Yeah.
In my opinion, it's
chock-full of treasures.
I couldn't agree more!
Manoyama's full
of hidden riches!
I still think we need something
with a pretty dramatic impact
to express that to people
who don't already know it.
So, you wanna use food
to revive the town.
What if I made a list of
all the seasonal ingredients
that I use from Manoyama
and sent it to you,
would that help?
Oh, would you, really?
Sure, that's easy.
Ingredients by the season...
That gives me an idea.
What if we have the
C-Rank Gourmet dish
change with seasons?
Wow, you're past your
instant ramen phase.
Whatever, Miss Sandwich!
Wait a minute, maybe you
and I should team up!
We'd put things together that
nobody else would think of!
I love it!
I have a feeling we're gonna
make the Queen eat her words!
Yeah, well, we'll
see about that!
I can't get over the fact
that you went to France
right after high school.
That's so cool and
incredibly brave!
I didn't really think
about it. I just kinda left.
What was my sister like
back when you guys
went to school together?
Ah. Oh, well,
she was really cute.
And she was smart
and friendly, too.
She was quite popular back then.
Huh.
Whereas, I was always
a pretty average guy,
so it was difficult
to get to know her.
Don't be so silly,
that can't be true!
[SANAE] Those two are
getting along pretty well.
Shiori, irresistible
to older men.
Oh, come on.
But look at him,
he's so into her!
[MAKI]
Maybe she's not an airhead.
[RIRIKO]
No, no, she's not dumb at all.
Shii- chan knows
what she's doing.
Would you stop?
She can hear you!
I see.
I actually kind of assumed
that you two must have dated.
Wha--?
I mean, you guys were
definitely acting weird
at the restaurant.
Oh, gosh, no. No way!
If we had been, I would
never have left her
and gone to France.
But, anyway, none of
this matters because
she never showed up.
Never showed up where?
I'm not coming up with
any dishes at all.
Tell me something,
is it just me or do people
seem to eat somen a lot here?
It's a local thing.
Then why isn't it on
this list from Mr. Bear?
My guess is that they don't
use it in French food.
Yeah, that makes sense.
So, hey, what do you think?
You think those two will
end up going out at all?
You mean Mr. Bear and Shiori?
I do think they'd
make a good couple.
Wish we could talk
about our love lives,
but that's a short conversation.
[MAKI]
Right?
I fear we've missed the
mark, yet again, chefs.
Tropical Shish-kebab?
Frozen Fried Rice?
Defeated-Samurai Manju ?
Where are the local ingredients?
Did you guys even
refer to Kumano's list?
Let's showcase
Manoyama's products!
If the people in
Manoyama won't accept it,
I don't think it'll
ever catch on!
So what did you make?
I made a pumpkin ohagi .
I featured both
rice and pumpkins
that are grown in Manoyama.
You can't tell that
by looking at it.
Yeah, it's pretty boring.
You guys keep telling me that.
So I guess I don't
have much of a sense
of what's boring and what isn't.
But out of all of us,
there's no question you're
by far the best cook.
So, I still think you
should lead the project.
I'm so sorry, but I really
don't think I can do it.
Awkward.
Anyone have a clue
what to do next?
Well, I see, then.
Sounds like that chef
took you seriously.
[SHIORI]
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Oh, thanks. Hi, Dad.
Something wrong?
No. Why don't we go for
a little walk, though?
Heh, heh.
[SHIORI] Wow, it's been a
long time since we've just
taken a walk together,
hasn't it?
[TAKAYUKI] Yeah, too long.
So, kiddo, is there a guy?
Huh?
I want you to know that
I've got no problem at all
with that young man.
[gasps] What do you mean?
Well, it's just that you'll
be a bride someday,
and I think we should talk
about something important
before that happens.
Our neighbor, Takahashi,
said she's decided
to give up her farm.
[SHIORI]
Really?
[TAKAYUKI] At her age, it's
too hard to manage it alone.
And her son's got his
own life in Tokyo now.
[SHIORI]
How sad.
[TAKAYUKI] Your mother
and I are, thankfully,
still in good shape.
We'll be fine for
another ten years.
I'm just not sure
what'll happen next.
To get to the point,
I don't want you
or your future husband to feel
any pressure to take it over.
Luckily, we've all still
got good day jobs.
We'll be just fine
without the farm.
I don't want anything
to change, though, Dad.
I'm happy the way
things are, now.
Oh, sweet girl. Life is
about change and growth,
so don't be afraid
to embrace it.
[gasps]
[TAKAYUKI]
I want you to live your life
the way you want to live it.
I want you to love
who you love and live
wherever you want to live.
And I don't want
you to worry at all
about your mother and me.
[SHIORI] Sayuri, can I
talk to you for a sec?
Sure, come in.
Looks like you're almost done.
I know, shocking.
Not too bad for a chronic
procrastinator, huh?
Hey, what's up, sis?
You look kinda down.
[SAYURI]
Wow. That's a lot.
Yeah, it really did
take me off guard.
It sort of came out of nowhere.
I mean, I've honestly
never thought about
what my life would be
ten years from now.
I guess I was naive
enough to think
things would stay the same.
That's okay, though.
Don't beat yourself up for
not worrying about the future.
I mean, after all, Grandma,
Grandpa, Mom, and Dad,
worked hard so
we wouldn't worry.
I guess so.
Hey, is that your
high school yearbook?
Oh, yeah.
I've realilzed I don't know
much about anything yet.
About myself,
or about this family,
or even about our home town.
Kumano knows way more
about Manoyama than I do,
even though he's been
living in France.
He's sort of amazing, really.
I agree with you.
Actually, if I'm being honest,
I was pretty interested in him
back when we were
in high school.
Oh, really?
Yeah, I liked him.
But I guess it kind of
felt like we lived
in two different
worlds or something.
I found it hard to approach him.
The thing is, he was saying
the same thing about you.
What? Was he, really?
That's so weird. I wonder why
he didn't come like
he promised, then.
[gasps]
Hey, what's this inside?
[MINO] The boss went and had
it updated all on his own.
[YAMADA] He's meeting with
the company right now.
This is supposed to be "deluxe"?
Where's the old ass?
Get out here, old ass!
Mrs. Oribe!
[MINO]
Ah! Mrs. Oribe!
Can I help you with something?
You're damn right, you can!
What the hell am I
looking at, here?
Whatever possessed you
to hold this thing
on the same day as
our summer festival?
Are you all trying
to start a war?
It's the same day?
[CHITOSE] The Board
of Merchants hasn't heard
a single word about this!
Yoshino, you didn't tell them?
I am so sorry.
I've guess we've
just been so focused
on coming up with a dish.
Oh, so it's your fault.
I suppose I could've
guessed that.
You really go out of your
way to mess things up
around here, don't you, Queen?
Everything you people do is done
solely to please yourselves.
None of the locals
asked for any of this.
None of us want it. At all!
[MINO]
This is bad.
It's an unwritten
rule that we check
with the Board of
Merchants before we do
basically anything at all.
People out here hate
being disrespected
and losing face more than
just about anything else.
What the hell was that?
I thought I heard the old
hag's voice a minute ago.
Has something happened?
[USHIMATSU] Oh, right.
I totally forgot about it.
Oh well. Let her be.
We can't do that.
Thanks to a certain someone,
our relationship is in ruins.
And here, I thought
the Board of Merchants
would be so pleased
with all of our plans.
But yet again, I'm reminded
I need to listen
to the people who live here.
I'm so sorry. Please forgive me.
Man, I really messed things up.
Hey, no worries, Yoshi!
And anyway, this
isn't all your fault.
Everyone is responsible.
We should've been paying
closer attention.
I think that we should all
go apologize together.
I wholeheartedly agree.
No way in hell I'm going.
You will if I have
to drag you myself.
[USHIMATSU grumbles]
Well, are you just going
to stand there all night?
No, ma'am.
We want to express our
most sincere apologies.
For failing to review
our schedule with you.
Mr. Kadota!
Yeah, we're sorry.
I mean, what can I say that
hasn't already been said?
These kids, you know,
they weren't really thinking.
But they didn't mean any harm.
So, please don't
hold it against them.
[CHITOSE] Listen.
I've got something to say.
It's always been the same
with the Tourism Board.
You never ask our opinion.
You just do what you want.
Twenty years ago, you hopped
on that stupid bandwagon,
and changed the
kingdom of Kabura
to the kingdom of Chupakabura.
And to top it off,
you started selling
that bizarre manju .
Okay, fine, I could
deal with that.
But now, what have you done?
Well I've heard
you're trying to make
a new version of that
manju . Is that right?
[USHIMATSU]
So what's it to you, hag?
I dealt with all of
your nonsense because
you were at least using products
that were made in Manoyama.
But now you're working with
some new company, huh?
What is it you're
trying to do here?
And where was that wheat
grown, and the azuki beans?
You've been using cheap imports
that have no
connection to Manoyama!
But as long as
you can get people
to come to your kingdom,
you'll consider that a
big success, won't you?
Do you honestly think that
helps revive the town?
I think I've heard enough now.
You listen here!
We can only grow this
town with more people!
Nothing we do here matters
if the town has no future!
Mr. Kadota, please, stop!
This is not helping!
C'mon, we came
here to apologize.
More importantly,
how do you plan to
address the current problem?
Can I assume you'll be changing
the date of your event?
[USHIMATSU]
It's too late for that!
Then why the hell
did you come here?
I'm so sorry.
I'm really responsible
for all of this.
Yes, and I'm asking how
you're going to take
that responsibility.
It requires more
than an apology!
The special presentation...
...will be canc--
No, we can't!
We have to!
Please, give me some time
to think of a solution.
Something that works
for everybody--
benefiting the Tourism Board.
And the Board of
Merchants, too. No.
Something with the needs of
everyone in Manoyama in mind!
Well, Shi.
Do you really think
you can do that?
Yes I can.
I will lift this burden
off of the Queen,
and I'll commit to take
the lead on this project.
[SANDAL] Cropeacur Yakisoba
is surprisingly tasty!
So, everyone, please try
it at your own risk.
Next time: "The Lady's Scales."