[USHIMATSU growling]
[USHIMATSU]
What do you think?
Not bad for being made
20 years ago, huh?
Uh, yeah...
It's a sci-fi film set in the
Kingdom of Chupakabura.
Yeah, I created it.
Pitched it to some
production companies.
[MAKI]
Uh-oh, it cut off.
They apparently ran
out of funding part way
through filming,
so that's as far as they got.
I think that might've been
a blessing in disguise.
I know, right?
[USHIMATSU]
What's that supposed to mean?
[YOSHINO] The scripts for the
movie just got here, you guys!
[SHIORI] This time it'll be run
by an actual production company!
And the cool thing is,
they approached us
about shooting in Manoyama!
Why wouldn't they?
What time is the
film crew getting here?
It can't be long now.
A slice-of-life story
set in Manoyama.
This is such great P.R.!
I bet it'll bring in
more tourists!
Yes! There it is!
They've got my name in there.
Will you actually
appear in the movie?
[USHIMATSU] They didn't
have enough actors.
What can you do?
So you used your position
to force your way in, huh?
[SANAE]
If that's the case,
maybe you could score
a role with lines,
Little Miss Oden.
Little Miss what, now?
I don't act anymore.
The lead is Taiga Hayama,
and the heroine is Moe Sawano.
I've never heard of her before,
but I've seen Taiga Hayama in
lots of dramas and commercials.
This'll be my first
time to meet a real actor!
Oh, yeah,
chief handywoman.
Yo, Maki!
[MAKI]
Hm?
[USHIMATSU] Heard they're
short on stagehands.
You could do that, right?
Huh?
They're saying people with
past production experience
would be real handy.
[MAKI]
Well, you can forget it.
Wha--?
What was that?
[FUJIWARA]
You must be Ms. Shinomiya.
Thanks for setting up
housing for us.
My pleasure.
My name's Fujiwara.
I'm the 3rd assistant director.
The director got tied up
with something,
so he'll be here
a little later on.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I don't have a card
to give to you.
I'm Yoshino Koharu, Queen of the
Kingdom of Chupakabura.
It's great to meet you.
Ah!
One of those tourism
ambassadors, huh?
Basically, yeah!
Cool, we've got
a queen on our side!
I'm sure that'll come in handy!
Uh, good!
You should be in that movie,
Oden Detective.
No, I shouldn't.
Oh, okay.
Maybe I'll go
try to grab a role.
Well, that'd make it
a whole different genre
for sure.
[TAKAMIZAWA] Hey, where
are the two of you going?
[ERIKA]
Taiko practice.
Kill me now.
So why not take a role
as an extra instead?
Your big film debut!
I don't work for free.
O... kay.
[door opens]
[BOYO]
Hey, Kosuke!
Well, hey there!
Practice, huh?
I'm right behind you--
be there in a bit.
Practice hard!
Uh, yeah.
I'll try to do that.
Huh...
[TAKAMIZAWA]
"Average luck"? Really?
[KOSUKE] Can I get a
melon au lait, please?
[GROUP snoring]
[YOSHINO] So what exactly
do you need us to do for you?
Ah, let's see here.
To start, we'll need to
negotiate for the location,
talk to the residents,
apply for a road use
permit with the police,
secure some extras,
set up catering.
[YOSHINO]
Wha--?
The assistant director's
in charge of all that stuff?
Yeah, and I'm only third in line
behind the chief
and first assistant.
Plus, we have to
share the workload
because we have a
super small budget.
Wow, that must
be pretty rough.
[FUJIWARA]
Kinda.
There are definitely things
I won't be able to get to,
so we're really going
to need as much help
as you can give us!
No worries, friend.
Between all of us,
we can handle it.
Thanks, I hope so.
[KOSUKE] How long are you
planning on staying over there?
Dunno. It's pretty comfortable.
[KOSUKE]
Don't be so stubborn.
Just come home.
[MAKI]
I'm sure he's still pissed off.
You mean Dad?
What, about you
dropping out of college?
[MAKI]
Mm-hmm.
I didn't wanna go
in the first place.
I wanted to go to art school.
Yeah.
He did have predictably
strong feelings about that.
You think?
[KOSUKE] Probably just
a little hurt that you didn't
consult with him
before you quit.
Old man's got a lot
of pride, you know.
Wait, whose side
are you on, anyway?
Come on, apologize
and get it over with.
Huh? What am I supposed
to apologize for?
I'm not gonna pretend
I was the wrong one.
Damnit, Maki.
And what about you,
brother of mine?
This is your last year.
Are you planning on leaving
town when I go back?
Hey, don't worry about me.
I like this town a lot.
You know how I do.
Drummin' my way through it all.
[MAKI] That's exactly
what I am worried about.
What I'm thinking is they could
come down this way on the bikes,
like so.
It'd be a better composition
if we could shoot
from the other side, though.
What do you think?
Where would we set up
the base camp?
[YOSHINO]
Sanae! Check it out!
[SANAE screams]
Stop that! How old are you?
--[YOSHINO laughs]
--Yoshi, let's go,
we should get to
work now, anyway.
[YOSHINO]
Aww! Hi!
Whatcha doin' there,
little buddy?
[CAT meows]
[SANAE] It's pretty empty,
but it's got great atmosphere.
These streets have been
here since the Edo period!
[ASST DIRECTOR]
Even a water mill!
What a score!
Yes, this particular
mill is being powered
to grind buckwheat!
Aw, yeah! I got the shot!
What, you're a director now?
I gotta tell ya,
I never noticed how beautiful
Manoyama really is.
[SHIORI]
I'm glad to hear you say that.
The cool thing is that
you've got a bunch of
great filming locations all
packed into a small area!
Makes life so much
easier for everyone
working on the shoot, you know?
I'm happy to hear that.
But I... feel like
I should apologize.
For this weird stuff.
No, no, no.
This is perfect
for what we need.
What kind of movie is this?
[ASST DIRECTOR]
Hey, Fujiwara!
Brace yourself.
Our dear director
is messing around
with the plotline again.
[FUJIWARA]
What? Not again!
Why have you all
come barging in here?
There's no window
shopping allowed.
I know this is kind of
a sudden request,
but is there any
possibility you'd consider
letting us film here?
The director's looking
to shoot in a shop
that has a real historic feel.
[SANAE] This is the only
place we could think of
that fit the bill.
No other shop like it in town!
Hmm. Is that so?
Also, the head of
the tourism board
already gave us permission
to shoot wherever we like.
[YOSHINO, SANAE gasp]
[CHITOSE]
Huh?!
The person who told you
that is obviously an imbecile!
I'm the head of
the Board of Merchants!
Show a little respect!
It's not like I'll benefit
from helping you out!
You'll only get in the
way of our business!
Go on, get out of here!
[YOSHINO]
Please, ma'am!
[CHITOSE]
Come back yesterday!
Head of the tourism board.
I'm not going to let that
old ass have his way.
Omanju .
[CHITOSE]
Huh?
They're going to have
omanju in the movie.
If you say no, they'll have
to use Chupakabura manju .
Are you serious?
Then the worst of Manoyama
would be on full display!
Hey! Come back here!
[GROUP snoring]
[YOSHINO]
I'm not really sure how,
but that worked out well!
Yeah, man, that was kinda close.
And it's been just like
that for days now.
One thing after another.
He drove all night from Tokyo
and worked all day
without any breaks.
Wow, the film industry
sounds really tough, huh?
Has it ever gotten
to the point where
you've wanted to quit?
Oh, sure, I've wanted
to quit plenty of times.
But nah, no shoot
lasts forever, you know?
And really, when it
comes down to it,
I love this job.
I'd never quit.
[YOSHINO]
So this is the house, huh?
It's impressive!
I'd say it was built
about sixty years ago.
The owners haven't
been living here
for a long time.
They said they
aren't coming back,
and that we can use
the house all we want!
The director's finally here!
It's good to see you, sir!
These are the nice folks
from the tourism board.
[YOSHINO] It's a pleasure
to meet you. I'm the--
Yeah, yeah, the pleasure's mine.
So is this the one, then? Hmm.
It's very tidy, don't you think?
Yes, sir.
When we found out it
would be used for the shoot,
we had some people volunteer,
and they cleaned it right up.
All the sliding doors have been
replaced, the drawers too!
[SHIORI]
It might be old,
but if you put in a
little work, anything--
[SONODA]
It's all wrong! Ugh!
It needs to be beaten up!
Why the hell would anybody
do something like this?
It's no good. We can't use it.
But sir, consider.
There's not a whole lot here.
Hey, there we go!
That one would be great!
It's beautifully worn down.
And it'll look gorgeous
as it burns to the ground!
It's settled!
We'll use that one.
Burns to the ground?
Yeah, on the final
day of the shoot,
we'll have to torch
the house for the climax!
[SHIORI gasps]
You'll burn it down for real?
I don't remember seeing
that scene in the script.
No, you can't use that house!
Uh, why?
Well, umm, because it's...
It's really haunted?
Yes! That's perfect!
Then it's ideal for
our haunted house story!
Haunted house story?
[SONODA]
Well, that seals the deal.
Get it handled by the
last day of the shoot.
And if you can't, you're gone!
All right! Next location!
[FUJIWARA]
Okay, I guess that's the plan.
[SONODA humming]
[SANAE]
Queen, what do you think?
Will it work?
Hey, Shiori, do you
know who owns the house
and where they are?
We need to ask their permission.
I'll take care of everything.
You've got a
million other things
to be worried about
right now, anyway.
[YOSHINO]
Thanks! I'll leave it to you.
Sorry about this, Kosuke.
No problem, it's from Mom.
Thank you. A lot. Really.
I'm off, then.
Gotta get back
before Dad finds out.
[MAKI] Mm-hmm.
Say hi to Mom for me!
[KOSUKE]
Yep!
[SANAE yawns] This day really
took it all out of me.
You know, our minister of Oden
could get off her butt
and help out a little.
Hey, be nice, Sanae.
No, she's just pouting
because Mr. Kadota said
she should be a stagehand.
Ignore her.
[YOSHINO]
Maki?
Hey. Welcome home.
I just got a care
package from my brother.
Wanna share?
Sorry. I'm a minister, too,
so I know I should
be working on this
just as hard as
everyone else is.
I know it must've
sucked for him to tell you
to be a stagehand
when you're an actor.
I totally get that.
That's not really
the problem, though.
Don't worry.
I'll cover for you as long
as you need to stay away.
The assistant director
said something earlier today.
His job's killing him,
but he sticks with it
'cause he loves it so much.
I realized I've never
had anything in my life
that I was that
passionate about.
I kinda envy him, you know?
Yeah, except loving it
is what makes it so hard.
[YASUDA]
Well, yes, we were related,
but only distant relatives.
The place ended up in our name
because there was nobody else
to leave it to.
You can go right ahead
and tear it down or burn it up
or do whatever you want.
It'd actually be helpful!
All right. Thank you so much.
[YASUDA]
My pleasure, dear.
[SHIORI] Well, that sure
didn't take long.
"Okay, everyone,
please calm down.
I can understand
why you're angry."
Feels a little stiff.
Who wrote this stuff, anyway?
"Okay everyone, all right.
Getting mad will only
make you hungry.
Here, why don't you have
one of these manju , 'kay?"
Yes, I'm calling about
the ten extras we requested.
Right, we'll need them here
all afternoon on Tuesday.
Great, I'll look forward
to seeing them then!
So the shoot starts tomorrow.
Of course the boss is ecstatic.
Don't remind me.
You know that was originally
supposed to be my role?
Pretty messed up, huh?
Look at him--he's seriously
like a little kid.
Hey, you're back!
Did everything with
the house go okay?
Oh, right.
I, uh...
Unfortunately, I wasn't
able to get in touch
with the owners like we'd hoped.
What?!
If we don't get it
by the last day,
it'll be a disaster!
Oh, what'll we do now?
Just calm yourself down, Queen.
There are plenty
of empty houses.
But we can't destroy
them without permission!
Well, they're all
on private property,
so having them demolished
can be pretty expensive.
That's why they're abandoned.
Even turning it
into an empty lot
raises the taxes.
A vicious cycle.
That's why we've got
to take this opportunity
to reduce their numbers--
these "haunted houses."
[MINO] Good. Why don't we
start with your house?
Oh, you're so funny,
what a guy... you idiot!
I'm talking about getting
the production company
to cover part of
the demolition bill!
That way it ends up a good
deal for the owners, too!
Is that true?
Okay, I'll look for
another empty house then!
Hopefully one that burns well!
If you don't find one,
use Mr. Kadota's, okay?
Or even if you do find one!
[USHIMATSU]
"Or even if you do." Shut up!
[taiko drums]
[KOSUKE]
That's it! Keep it up!
Yes! Love it!
We're adding a scene
with taiko drumming!
The plot is a living,
breathing thing, Fujiwara!
Have the extras
hold tight for now.
[CROWD chattering]
Shouldn't you guys be at work?
Yeah. Shouldn't you?
I am working.
I'm providing security
for the shoot.
Not me. I'm just a nerd.
The lead girl, Moe,
is such a doll!
I had no idea this many
people even lived here.
[SHIORI chuckles]
Welcome! Today we begin
principal photography on
The Forever Forest!
And now, it's my
honor to introduce you
to the cast!
In the lead role of Takeshi,
we have Taiga Hiyama!
Hey, everyone!
It's a pleasure to meet you all.
[FUJIWARA] And playing
the heroin, Naoko,
it's Moe Sawano!
Hi, everybody!
It's so great to be here!
[CROWD clapping]
What is all this
crappy make-up?
I just look like
I'm dead or something!
Well, more precisely,
the undead.
Okay, if I could get
your attention over here!
When I give the signal,
rush to the window
and don't forget to groan!
What? What do you mean, groan?
I'm supposed to
have a real line!
Nope!
All you need to do is groan.
What the hell is
my part here, kid?
[CHITOSE laughing]
He won't die in real life,
and now he's a zombie!
This is poetry!
[SONODA]
And, action!
Takeshi!
You can't go outside!
You have to survive this!
You have to!
I want you to
wait here for me!
--[FILM EXTRAS moaning]
--[USHIMATSU growling]
[MOE gasps]
If I don't get the medicine,
we can't save the city.
No, please!
Don't leave me behind!
I was thinking, if I
make it back from this...
...let's get married.
[TAIGA yells]
[FILM EXTRAS growling]
[MOE screams]
Nice! And, cut!
All right, let's review it!
You know, that old man
is actually not too bad.
Hi, there. Can I help you?
A super high sensitive SLR
with a 5-axis brushless gimbal.
[YOSHINO]
Mr. Sonoda, about the house
you were looking
at the other day.
We couldn't get in touch
with the owners,
but we're looking for
another house now.
Out of the thirteen
houses we've found,
we've been able
to reach the owners
--of six of them so far--
--[SONODA] No, that won't do!
The location, the atmosphere--
it's gotta be that one!
I can already see
the shot in my head, so
you'll just have
to work it out.
But I--I'll see what I can do.
[ASST DIRECTOR] Okay,
we're heading to Sakura Pond!
He can yell all he wants--
we still won't get it.
[FUJIWARA]
Okay.
Yeah, if she can't, she can't.
We'll figure something out here.
Bye.
I can't believe
she's backing out
after all the fuss they
made to put her in it.
Hey, what happened?
Sudden cancellation.
An actress set to
join the shoot today.
What?
[FUJIWARA] She wore heels
while hiking up Mt. Takao
and broke her leg.
Why the hell would she do that
the day before the shoot?
Wow, so what're you gonna do?
Luckily, it's a small role
with just a couple of lines.
But the problem is
the scene really won't work
without it.
I am so screwed.
Hey, Queen.
[YOSHINO]
Oh, Ririko!
Um, I just saw Maki, and--
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
Maki!
[MAKI]
A stand-in?
Yep!
I told them you were
the only one in town
who could do it!
And it's a really
good role, too.
She has lines and everything!
Good luck!
What the hell do you
mean, "good luck"?
I never asked for your help!
What the heck?
Then my next film
was a big blockbuster.
What, are you playing
a zombie today, too?
Yeah, basically, yeah.
[YOSHINO]
I don't know.
I guess that means
I must've said something
I shouldn't have.
[SANAE]
No, you didn't!
This is not your fault!
She's such a total hypocrite!
Preaching about
not running away.
[SHIORI]
Where are you going?
I'm going to set her straight!
She's not even
helping out anymore.
It's time to grow up!
[MOE]
Maki?
Oh, my gosh,
it really is you, Maki!
Hey, Moe.
So what are you doing here?
Oh, please tell me you're
working on this movie, too.
'Cause that means
we get to work together!
Oh, no, this is
just my hometown, so...
I happen to be staying
at home for a while.
[MOE]
Oh, that's cool.
I snuck off to take a
little walk on my own
to try and get a feel
for the place.
It really is a lovely area.
Seems you've been
doing well lately.
I keep seeing you
in movies and dramas.
Well, I'm still
an unknown, though.
[MOE] So when are you
coming back to Tokyo?
Ooh! We should go have
lunch or something!
[MAKI]
The thing is, I left the agency.
[MOE] But you haven't
given up on being an actor,
have you?
I don't know.
I don't know much
of anything right now.
I can't pretend to
know what happened,
but I really do hope
you decide to stick with it.
I've always loved your acting.
I truly mean that.
[ISOGAI]
What are you doing here?
You can't wander off
like that on your own
without telling me, Moe!
[MOE]
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll see you 'round, Maki! Bye!
[MOE] Sorry, I hope you
weren't too worried!
[ISOGAI] Just give me
a heads-up next time.
[MOE]
I will.
[SANAE] So she joined
the same agency after you?
[MAKI]
Yeah, she did.
[SANAE] And now she's
gotten ahead of you.
Tell me something.
Have you ever eaten a cicada?
[SANAE]
What?
Well, she did. On TV.
You've seen it on
game shows right?
How they make people
eat weird stuff?
Down the hatch, little bug!
[CONTESTANTS gasp, squeal]
The way I see it,
it's not something you get
to experience every day,
you know?
And if doing this show can
get me more opportunities
as an actor, I'm basically
willing to do anything.
Sure enough,
people talked about it,
and that was how
she ended up getting
her big break.
But you're invested.
You took all those
part time jobs to study
for roles, didn't you?
But I wouldn't eat
the damn cicada!
I guess that just goes
to show ya
I wasn't as committed
to being an actor
as I should've been.
I think I only wanted to perform
because I was praised
for it as a kid,
but I'm through with it.
That whole world.
Are you serious?
[MAKI]
I'm grown up and I'm broke.
If I got my first
role at this point,
I think I'd be embarrassed.
I know they say stick
with it if you love it.
But isn't that like
an abusive relationship?
There's no future for me there.
Your twenties
are a special time.
I kinda wasted mine.
But at least I've
realized it now, huh?
I'm gonna try to search really
hard for what I want to do.
[SANAE]
How pathetic.
What?
[SANAE]
I can understand setbacks
and wanting to take a break.
I'm in the same boat, after all.
But when you choose
to reject something
that you know you
love so passionately,
it's disgraceful.
Also, you need to
apologize to Yoshino.
You've... You've got to...
You've gotta survive!
Takeshi!
[SANDAL] I have a coffee table
book about Taiga Hiyama.
I accidentally bought it online.
Next time:
"The Mansion in Purgatory."