[CROWD clapping]
[YOSHINO] I think it's
a memory from my childhood.
I was in the main hall
of a palace somewhere.
Surrounded by my people
who were shouting my name.
And I wore a beautiful,
sparkling crown on my head.
[YOSHINO] In that moment,
I felt so happy.
It was perfect.
Was it some kind of dream?
Or did that day really happen?
I'm still not completely sure.
But it's my favorite memory!
[PROCTOR A] You're saying that
one memory has made you happier
than anything else in your life?
Uh, yes!
[YOSHINO]
Oh, crap! I screwed it up!
[PROCTOR A] I see you've applied
for our management track,
but are you open to accepting
a secretarial position?
Sure!
Yes, I'm open to that.
I'd be proud to do my
part in any way I could.
[PROCTOR A]
Even at a rural branch?
Well, I'm not gonna lie.
I'd prefer Tokyo.
How many applications
have you submitted so far?
About thirty, counting this one.
[PROCTOR B] Considering that,
what's your theory
as to why none of
the others have offered you
a position yet?
Heh...
[FORTUNE TELLER 1A] Your human
strokes and total strokes
are unlucky, but the heaven
strokes are quite good.
Your golden years
will be blessed.
Look, I don't care
about my golden years!
I want to be blessed now!
[phone chiming]
[sighs]
Anything wrong, Miss?
[YOSHINO] Yep. I've just been
"wished the best of luck" again.
It's like, I can't even seem
to nab a normal job
in the real world,
let alone be anyone's queen.
[YAE] You can always come back
here if it doesn't work out.
Why don't you come home
and give your poor Mom
a hand?
You're saying I should
move home and help you out
with the chores?
You know the last thing
I want is to grow old
in the country.
[YAE] But you're okay with
growing old in the city?
[YOSHINO sighs]
[YAE] It's what normal
people do, you know.
What's wrong with being normal?
Can you please not
call me "normal"?
I mean, I didn't say I was
completely out of options here.
I just had an interview today
and I haven't heard back yet.
[YAE] Why are you so
set on staying in Tokyo?
There's plenty of
work out here, too.
I don't like the countryside.
I'm not coming home, okay?
And that's that!
[YAE]
Fine.
But a graduate's gotta
go somewhere, right?
Remember, this is the
last month we're sending you
an allowance!
Ugh. What was I thinking,
having my fortune told
when I'm this broke?
[squeals]
I wonder if mayonnaise
would be tasty
or truly disgusting on this?
[phone ringing]
[YOSHINO]
Yeah, hello?
[HASHIMOTO]
Good evening!
Tell me, have I reached
Yoshino Koharu's cellphone?
You have.
This is her speaking.
[HASHIMOTO]
Great, this is Hashimoto
with Momonga Promotion Agency.
I'm sorry. With which agency?
[HASHIMOTO] Momonga,
the model placement agency.
You registered
with us a while back
and we were able to place you
on a small project, remember?
Oh! Yeah, of course!
My friend and I
registered together
and you sent me on that job.
[HASHIMOTO] Well, we actually
had a client request you
by name, Ms. Koharu.
To be the spokesperson
for a rural town's
promo campaign.
They want you to be their queen.
Be their queen?
Wait, you mean like
mayor-for-a-day type thing?
[HASHIMOTO chuckles]
The job is with a tourism board,
so it's probably something
along those lines.
There are obviously more
details in the contract.
We'll send money to cover all
of your travel and expenses,
--of course.
--[YOSHINO] Hey, slow down.
I haven't agreed yet!
[HASHIMOTO]
Oh, Ms. Koharu,
you graduated from junior
college this spring, right?
Have you already found a job?
[YOSHINO]
Well, no. Good point.
There's nothing here.
Hard to imagine
a tourist attraction.
Oh, hold on.
Could I have gotten
on the wrong train?
[gasps]
[YOSHINO]
So sorry!
Um, 'scuse me,
but can you tell me,
is this the correct train
for Manoyama?
[MAKI]
Manoyama? Why go there?
For a job. I'm from Tokyo.
A job in Manoyama, huh?
[YOSHINO]
Yeah.
They've asked me
to be their queen.
Oh, the Chupakabura thing.
[YOSHINO]
Uh...
Anyway, is this train--?
[CONDUCTOR 1A]
Next stop: Manoyama Station.
Manoyama.
Hi! Thanks for meeting me!
I'm Yoshino Koharu from Momonga!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
Hmm? What is this?
I'll slow down.
My name is Yoshino Koharu
and I'm here to take the job.
You know, the one as the queen?
Koharu?
[SHIORI]
I'm so sorry.
There appears to have been
some kind of mix-up.
The person we were trying
to request for the position
is named Yoshino Tsubaki.
Yoshino Tsubaki?
Oh, she apparently
used to be a big pop star
back in the day.
Our board director
is a huge fan,
so he planned to have her
come promote our town
as queen.
[USHIMATSU] That person out
there is not my little Yoshino!
How in the hell did you
manage to screw this up?
Well, if you look at your note,
it really doesn't look
at all like Tsubaki.
Oh, it's my fault?!
Ah, here we are.
I finally found some info
on Yoshino Tsubaki.
I'm afraid she passed
away eight years ago.
[USHIMATSU]
Wha--?
Wow, so she was
famous forever ago.
What should we do now?
We already mailed off
that long application
to receive a subsidy!
And we've already transferred
the contract fees
to her agency.
Which is all your fault
because you screwed up!
[YAMADA] Seriously,
would you look at your note?
Well the banner said "Tsubaki,"
so how do you explain that?
Funny thing--that was
actually a mistake
'cause we asked for Koharu.
[USHIMATSU] The characters
are too close for Koharu!
Shigaraki is only
a novice calligrapher.
Well, I'm a master!
[YOSHINO] Holy cow,
these people are nuts.
Mr. Kadota, please,
you've gotta calm down!
You're being very rude
to Ms. Koharu!
After all, she came here for us.
Would you shut up, Shiori?
This random girl can't
possibly hold a candle
to my little Yoshino!
Your "little Yoshino"
would be an old woman
if she was alive!
Yeah, it's confusing
how you keep calling her
"little Yoshino."
What's confusing about Yoshino?
[YAMADA]
Everything!
[YOSHINO]
So, it's happened again.
Yet another job rejection.
She'll be my
"little Yoshino" till I die!
Pardon me!
[USHIMATSU]
Hm?
Um, the thing is,
we all know it's very easy
to mistake Tsubaki for Koharu
because of how they're written,
and no matter what level
calligrapher wrote it,
of course you would
see it as Tsubaki
if that's what you're
looking for from the start,
so that's no one's fault.
And no matter how old
your favorite pop star gets,
calling her "my little Yoshino"
is kind of sweet, isn't it?
Yeah, so, that's all okay.
Anyway...
I know I'm very young.
And I know I'm not
who you wanted.
And I'm sure Yoshino Tsubaki
was a wonderful person
and I couldn't hope to
compete with a pop star,
but if there is
something I could do
to help you all out here,
I'd love the
opportunity to try--
Fine, then!
I guess it's meant to be.
We'll go ahead
with the coronation,
as was originally planned.
[MINO]
Huh?
[SHIORI]
For the record...
I'm really glad it worked
out for you to stay.
Oh, my name is Shiori Shinomiya!
I work for the
tourism board, also.
Nice to meetcha.
[YOSHINO]
Thanks, you too!
The one walking up
in the front up there?
That's Ushimatsu Kadota.
He's the king.
He's also head of the board.
And behind him is Shigaraki,
the bureau chief.
The really young one
is named Yamada.
And the one with
the glasses is Mino.
[YOSHINO] This place is almost
as dead as back home.
Excellent. Is this another
one of your idiotic plans,
you old jackass?
Shut up, you stupid hag.
[YOSHINO gasps]
Oh, no worries!
Those two are always like that.
[SHIORI]
This is Sakura Pond.
Soon the blossoms
will be in full bloom,
and I promise you,
it's absolutely beautiful!
Oh, and if you look that way,
you can see the,
um, palace, over there.
[YOSHINO]
The palace?
The Kingdom of... Chupakabura.
[SHIORI] I know the kingdom
thing is pretty silly.
but they say years ago,
we used to get quite
a lot of tourists here
because of it!
A while back, these mini
independent states
were popping up
constantly all over Japan.
[YOSHINO]
Really? I never knew that.
It created interest in the town.
We received tax money as part
of the Hometown Revival project.
Manoyama got caught
up in the boom,
and you're looking
at the result.
Then, the boom ended,
and so, here we are.
[music playing]
[USHIMATSU] Citizens of the
Kingdom, you must not forget!
You must never forget
the horror and calamity
visited upon us by
the Chupakabura!
Only the legendary
Sacred Sword could defeat it!
But, alas, the sword had
been sealed into stone,
and nobody had been
able to free it!
And that was when I,
Ushimatsu Kadota,
appeared on the scene
and though many had failed,
I miraculously freed the sword!
[SHIORI]
That's the basic backstory.
Oh, cool.
[USHIMATSU]
I stood resolutely against
the Chupakabura's attack,
cutting the beast down!
The Secret Sword
did not fail me! However...
Imagine him with a monster.
Probably soiled his pants!
[laughing]
[MINO]
Sorry, Mr. Kadota,
but if you could wrap this up...
[USHIMATSU growls]
Now, we shall conduct the
traditional coronation ceremony.
So, step forward, new queen.
Oh, right, here I am!
I lay this crown upon your head
as an acknowledgement
of your sovereign reign.
[grunts] And now, I hereby
declare you to be the new queen
of the Kingdom of Chupakabura!
[AUDIENCE clapping, chattering]
[GROUP laughing]
Well, you've sure had
a long day, haven't you?
You must be pretty worn out.
Oh, no, it wasn't
that bad, really.
Hey, Kinu!
What gives?
We're running out
of booze down here!
Oh, all right.
What's wrong, Queen? Drink up!
Here, gimme your glass!
Oh, thank you.
I know it's a bit late
for me to ask,
but what is a Chupakabura?
Well, it's a legendary
monster from around these parts.
They say it can suck
the blood out of livestock,
but I've heard that it's
actually just a weasel.
It is not.
When I was a kid,
I saw it with my own eyes.
Oh, God. You're not really gonna
start that nonsense again.
It's not nonsense!
Then where is the Chupakabura?
It's inside all of our hearts!
[laughing]
[TATSU] Say, that's
pretty tasty, isn't it?
Those potatoes
are a town specialty!
And we're known for
making other things, too!
But you should know
that the best thing
we've made by far
is the town itself!
The hope is you'll be able
to get the word out
about this great little place!
So, my queen.
I look forward
to working with you.
Wait. What do you mean?
How 'bout a toast?
Raise your glasses, get 'em up!
That's right!
To Manoyama and
its shining future!
Pitch black.
[SHIORI] I have to tell you,
I really am so glad
that you decided
to take the job, Yoshi.
Oh, sorry, is it okay
if I call you Yoshi?
Oh, um... mm-hmm.
Oh, good! And you can
just call me Shiori.
[giggles]
I hope you weren't
caught too off guard.
I know those old guys
can be pretty lively.
I'm used to it. I'm actually
from the country, too.
Oh, wow, this whole time
I thought you were from Tokyo!
The country wasn't for me.
I got out as soon as I could.
Why was that?
There's just nothing out there,
and it's so boring.
I didn't want to spend my
entire life out in the sticks
doing nothing at all.
Oh! There's nothing
wrong with that, though!
No worries.
I mean, I totally hear
what you're saying,
but I really love my hometown.
That's why I want so badly
to be able to share it
with the rest of the world.
[SHIORI] Back in the day,
this little place
was used as a dorm.
Mr. Kadota said
to feel free to choose
whichever room you want.
Well, I guess that covers it,
at least for today.
[YOSHINO]
Thanks so much!
I've really appreciated
all your help.
Can't wait to kick things
off with you tomorrow!
What'd she mean,
"kick things off"?
--[rustling]
--[YOSHINO gasps]
[MAKI groans]
[YOSHINO gasps]
--[MAKI] Hm?
--[YOSHINO] Uh...
Wait a minute.
What are you doing
in this place?
Aren't you the new queen?
[YOSHINO]
What am I--?
They said I should
spend the night here, so--
anyway, why are you here?
Well, I'm the... guess I'm
the manager or something.
Of what, though?
So you're the talent, right?
What, like,
a model or something?
Or maybe you're a pin-up
girl that didn't sell?
That can't be it.
How rude!
I'm here because
I seriously needed the money.
So this is just
a one-time thing.
[MAKI] Oh, then,
you're just a normal student?
Could you please
not call me "normal"?
[MAKI]
So an abnormal student?
[YOSHINO]
What? No! I'm not!
Okay, so, you're normal.
Anyway, I'm kinda impressed
that you decided
to come to this
little podunk village.
It's not much more than
an old ghost town now.
Well, I'm going back
as soon as I get paid.
The event I was hired for
happened earlier today.
Wait, what are
you talking about?
You can't leave.
The job's just starting.
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
No way!
Did no one tell you?
Yoshino Koharu,
20 years old, from Tokyo,
was crowned the new queen
of the Kingdom of Chupakabura.
One hundred and fifty people
gathered together today
to celebrate her coronation.
The new queen will take up
residence here for one year,
and she'll be
participating in various
promotional projects for the--
Wait a minute!
No one said it was a whole year!
[HASHIMOTO] Hello, Hashimoto
with Momonga Promotions.
Listen, I thought this
job was for one day!
Nobody ever said a word to me
about a year-long commitment!
What am I supposed to do now?
[HASHIMOTO]
Ah, Ms. Koharu!
I do believe those details
were in your contract.
My contract?
[YOSHINO]
Yep, there it is.
You have gotta be kidding me!
I can't stay for a year!
[HASHIMOTO] Well, it's a
little late to back out now.
I'm afraid we've already
signed the contract
with the tourism board.
Look, I don't care, okay?
How am I supposed
to live way out here
in the boonies?
[HASHIMOTO] But you'd
given up on finding work
before graduation.
I'm still waiting to hear
back from one company!
You had no right to
assume I'd given up already!
[HASHIMOTO]
Well, anyway,
just give it your best shot!
Talk soon!
--Wait! Don't go!
--[phone beeps]
You'd think a normal person
would read the contract.
I said I'm not normal.
So there you go.
But this place is nuts.
I'm outta here!
[YOSHINO]
Which way do I go?
Hey! You headed to the station?
[TAKAMIZAWA]
The bus depot.
You missed the last
bus to the station.
[YOSHINO]
No! Please, I'm begging you!
I've gotta get there!
Oh, come on,
do you really wanna be
the crazy lady on the bus?
[YOSHINO]
Sure, bring it on!
As long as it gets me to Tokyo!
[SANDAL]
Ask the bus and it'll hear you.
Or maybe not.
It doesn't actually
have ears, does it?
Nah.
But I do think it has a nose.
Can you imagine?
A big bus nose?
With, like, long nose
hairs sticking out of it?
Yeah, I gotta go.
[YOSHINO panting]
What? But it's only
ten o'clock at night!
[phone ringing]
Kinu! Bring it here!
Hey, Kadota!
The new queen just
said she was gonna
go back to Tokyo and ran
off towards the station.
Is everything cool?
She did what?
I'm not letting her out of this.
Shiori! You're coming with me!
[rustling]
[YOSHINO whimpering]
[YOSHINO yells]
[CHUPAKABURA groans]
[SHIORI screams]
Yoshi! Help me!
No! Please save me!
[YOSHINO]
Shiori?
[SHIORI]
Go on!
You have to pull
the Sacred Sword free!
Yoshi, you can do it!
I believe in you!
If you defeat the Chupakabura
with the Sacred Sword,
then you will truly
become our new queen!
[CHUPAKABURA growls]
[CHUPAKABURA growling]
Would you stop screwing around?
[USHIMATSU groaning]
[SHIORI]
Oh, Mr. Kadota!
[gasps]
I'm so sorry.
[KINU] Don't worry about it,
I know he's a handful.
It's because...
well really, it's because
we all love our town
as much as we do.
He's always saying
he wants nothing more
than to bring back
the life it once had.
[chuckles]
However, I'm not sure
he's going about it
the right way.
He thought if you
freed the sword
and experienced being a hero,
then you'd surely change
your mind about things
and stay here with us.
Don't feel like you
have to take the job
if you don't want to.
You're free to make
your own choices.
Why don't you go on
back to the dorm for now.
And then tomorrow you
can return home. 'Kay?
[SHIORI]
I wanna apologize.
That was so stupid of us.
I'm still really glad
you came here, Yoshi,
even if it was only for a day.
I always thought it'd
be fun to have someone
my same age as the queen.
Working together to
liven up the town again,
making it all it can be.
So that's why.
I wanted you to stay so badly
I agreed to that silly prank.
I understand.
Thank you.
It selfishly makes me feel
good to have been wanted.
Thanks again.
Have a good night!
Okay, sleep well.
You've gotta be kidding!
Okay, then.
Guess I'll stay here
till morning.
[YOSHINO]
Lotta history.
What is this?
No way, I've really
been here before?
This is the place where
that memory came from!
[SHIORI]
Yoshi, you stayed!
So does this mean that
you've changed your mind?
Wait, no, no, that's
not what's happening!
It's just that it was cold,
and I didn't have a blanket,
plus I'm still waiting to
hear back on one interview--
[phone chiming]
I take that back.
[crutch clanking]
So have you finally
made up your mind, then?
No, I have not!
[USHIMATSU]
If you're staying,
your first job
is waiting for you,
so let's hurry up
and get you to work.
[SANDAL] The queen
wants to return to Tokyo.
But Tokyo is a little
too far away.
Next time: "The Gathering
of the Five Champions."