[MOE]
Hey, Maki!
The last part,
the dance audition,
how'd it go for you?
Well, I think
I did the best I could.
Good! I'm so excited!
Now we'll get to act together!
Wow, so you
just assume you got it?
I wish I had your confidence!
This industry's
all about confidence
and determination!
[door opens]
Okay, then, everyone.
We appreciate your patience
and your time today.
Now, when I call your name,
if you would please
step forward.
Number three, Seyama.
Number five, Onoda.
Number eight, Fujisaki.
Number nine, Yoshida.
Number ten, Nakata.
Number twelve, Midorikawa.
Number thirteen, Yamamoto.
Number fifteen, Tsurumi.
If I just called your name,
then you're free to go.
Thanks for coming in.
[MOE]
Maki!
Hey, congratulations, Moe!
I knew you'd get it.
Oh, friend.
I hope it goes great.
I'll be watching you.
Bye.
[KOSUKE]
Oh, man. She didn't make it in.
[RIRIKO]
Hello...?
Okay, this sure
isn't a great feeling.
It's hard to believe
nobody showed at all.
Maybe we didn't
give enough notice?
[MAKI]
Ms. Koharu!
Feed my belly, I'm hungry!
--Hey, Maki.
--[MAKI] Yo.
That was really fast!
Yep, a lot faster
than I expected.
I didn't get the part,
so I just came right back.
I'm finished with acting,
so from now on,
I'll focus on my role
as Chief Handywoman!
And I look forward
to working with all of you
once again!
Well, in that case...
I guess it's time to eat!
Mmm! This is great!
Well done, Chef Shinomiya!
Thanks, guys!
Doesn't mean much if
nobody comes, though.
It's the curse of
the Blood-Soaked Santa.
Oh, please, can we not?
You know, seems like nobody
cares about this school.
I wonder why.
Maybe it has to do
with the fact
that it never really closed.
Huh?
I just mean, I was in
the last graduating class
of this school,
but there was never any
closing ceremony.
Closing ceremony?
Like an event
to let everyone know
they're closing the school.
So the graduates can
get together and stuff.
Right. Opinions were
divided over whether
we should close it or not,
so we ended up having our
graduation ceremony,
and that was it.
Oh, so, that's what you meant.
"Never really closed."
Yeah.
Without closure,
you can't move on.
[USHIMATSU]
A closing ceremony?
[YOSHINO]
Yes!
It's been exactly ten years
since it was closed.
So we can really make
a big deal about it!
We wanna try to contact
as many graduates
as we can who have
since moved away.
[USHIMATSU] Well, first, how did
the whole hot lunch thing go?
Oh, yeah, that.
It didn't go so well.
[USHIMATSU]
You see? What'd I tell you?
You needed fried bread
on the menu!
You know, I graduated
from that school, too.
If you really did hold a
ceremony, I'd want to go.
But hey, are you
ready for the festival?
Very good point!
The Tourism Board
shouldn't be holding
a school's closing
ceremony to begin with!
Yeah, that's true,
but instead of just waiting
for it to be demolished,
this would be
a good opportunity.
We can look at how we might
repurpose the building
in a positive way.
[SANAE]
Which could, in turn,
potentially contribute to
increased activity in town.
We'll keep getting prepared
for the festival, too,
I swear. Please let us do this!
Well, let me think.
Just kidding! Go for it!
[YOSHINO]
So, yes, it's a ceremony,
but stirring up nostalgic
feelings won't be enough!
Well, we've already suggested
reusing the building.
I wonder what's
wrong with Sandal.
Besides eating
shaved ice in winter?
If you eat all of the snow,
spring will come.
[MAKI]
Huh?
[ANGELICA] He's upset
because the snow keeps him
from drawing outside.
I want a studio more than
anything in the world.
Please, send me
a lottery ticket!
You might want to ask
for the winning one.
The more the snow piles up,
the fewer customers we get.
I hear you. It's a bad
season for buses, too.
[ANGELICA,TAKAMIZAWA sigh]
Hey, snap out of it, you guys!
[RIRIKO]
♪ Sleep tonight, go and dream ♪
Oh, is that from
the other day?
Yeah.
Wow, look at that!
You've already got several
views, Riichan!
She's got a real pretty voice,
right, sis?
Uh... Yeah, I guess.
Thank you for saying that.
[ANJI] I don't know what
it's about, though.
[ERIKA]
Don't look at me.
Ugh.
It's true, it's kinda
hard to tell
what the original story
is from the song.
Ugh.
[ERIKA]
Ugh, huh?
We don't need you
getting upset, too.
That's gotta be
an easy fix, right?
[KOSUKE]
Melon au lait.
[ERIKA]
Coming right up!
What's up with you, Kosuke?
[KOSUKE] I was talking to
my friend about our futures.
He said he was leaving town.
"What's good about
Manoyama, anyway?
There are no movie theatres,
no music venues,
blah blah blah."
So then I was like, "You idiot!
We've got taiko drumming!"
I mean, if people want to go,
they should go, but I'm not.
That's all there
really is to it.
But why does he have to
get all critical like that?
Ugh!
[KOSUKE, ERIKA sigh]
[ANGELICA,TAKAMIZAWA sigh]
Hey, now, come on!
What's wrong with
you guys today?
[SANAE]
Oh, I see.
Turning the art room
into a studio, huh?
[YOSHINO]
Yeah!
It can be used until
it's demolished, right?
This is wonderful!
You can even have my
year-end lottery ticket.
That's quite a deal
if it's the winning one.
It'd be such a waste if we
didn't use the music room, too.
And this is great for
the Dondoko Taiko Club practice!
And maybe before long,
people will get creative
and want to show movies
or have live music events here!
If there's nothing
to do in town,
we need to create things to do!
[SHIORI]
That's right!
First, let's figure
out the ceremony.
Yoshino, you finish
the application yet?
Sure did!
However, before we deliver it
to the Board of Education,
there's someone I really
want us to visit.
[IWAO] Hmm...
A closing ceremony. Okay.
[YOSHINO] You've been in
education for a long time,
so we thought it might be
helpful to ask your advice
on this.
Yeah. Not a bad idea.
The Board will
probably surprise you.
They're not near
as stiff as you think.
I doubt they'd say no
to a proposal like this.
You think so?
[IWAO] When will you
take it to them?
If you'd like, I can go
with you when you do.
Would you really?
After all, rural politics are
really all about connections,
you know.
[GROUP]
Thank you, Mr. Midorikawa!
Yes, we appreciate your help.
By the way,
what's this thing?
What's the "Second Middle
Memorial Stage"?
Oh, that's just a--
[IWAO] Are you planning to
have something go on there?
You should probably
be more specific about it.
Sure! Yeah, we'll,
uh--That's it!
You know what people remember?
The Blood-Soaked Santa!
--[GROUP] What?
--We can put on a play!
I mean, after all, it's gonna
be right around Christmas!
Yeah, but what about the
part where he's blood soaked?
[YOSHINO]
We'll free his ghost!
Hold on a second, what do
you mean, "free his ghost"?
The director of the play will
be our Chief Handywoman, Maki!
So, we'll be in
very good hands!
Yoshino! You never even--Ugh!
Oh, good!
Well, if that's the case...
[SANAE]
It sure has piled up, huh?
It's not actually that much.
It'll probably melt pretty soon.
[RIRIKO] Right, winter doesn't
really start until the new year.
All units, attack!
[GROUP laughing]
[MAKI] Really, Queen?
What're you doing?
[yelps]
Oh, the queen's been hit!
Medic! Queen down!
This is no time
for us to be playing!
Do you realize how many
days are left till Christmas?
Whoa, Maki.
If we're gonna do this,
we're gonna do it right.
There's no way
I'm half-assing it.
Cool!
You guys are actually
pretty lucky to have found me!
Don't like to brag,
but I played the lead
a lot in elementary school.
I was in the ping pong club,
does that help?
And you're unemployed,
so you're not busy.
You're not busy, either.
I'm kinda surprised
to hear you did drama
in high school, Yamada!
Mr. Kadota stole
my role in the movie,
so I want another chance!
Sweet justice!
I'd really like
to thank my senpai
from my old acting troupe.
There's no way we'd
ever turn down a request
from our lovely friend, Maki!
Yeah, let's kick some butt!
The show must go on, guys!
Let's keep up the good work!
[SHIORI]
We haven't actually started yet.
[MAKI] Well, we don't have a
lotta time to put this together,
but we're gonna give it
our best shot.
I'm counting on you!
--[MAKI] Thank you.
--You gonna stay up?
[MAKI]
Yeah, a bit longer.
When you write
the script yourself
and you're also
an actor in the show,
you change things
till the last minute.
Interesting.
I'm kind of feeling like...
Like the Maki that
we've seen around here--
maybe she's just a tiny part
of who you really are.
Well, remember,
I had just come
back here in defeat.
You met me at my
very lowest point.
But I've finally
made up my mind.
No matter what I do
for work in the future,
I'll always try to bring
something I like to it.
I won't get upset
just because it may be
something I don't love.
Instead of complaining,
I'll try to infuse the situation
with creativity, you know?
Yeah, I get it.
I'm a little jealous, you see.
You have something
that you're passionate about
that keeps you going.
I wonder if I'll ever
find something like that.
Who knows?
Maybe you already have.
Ugh, what should I do?
What is it?
The last scene.
I want something to
really make an impact,
like, aside from the dialogue.
Really make an impact.
[GRADUATE 20A]
Ah, here it is!
I found us! Look!
[GRADUATE 20B]
Wow, that brings back memories!
You had a shaved head back then!
Oh, my.
Your graduating class
looks a bit lonely.
There were so many
more students here
back when I graduated.
Hurry, get in the shot, teacher!
[GRADUATES laugh]
Come on, now.
Sit down, you two crazies.
[SHIORI]
So many people came!
[YOSHINO]
Yeah.
It's time. All right,
you're up, Yoshino.
Greetings, Manoyama Second
Middle School graduates!
And welcome,
other friends of the school!
Thank you all.
The Closing Ceremony is for you!
For all of you!
We'd like to start the night
with a special greeting
from the school's last
principal, Mr. Yoshihiko Funazu.
Let's give him a
round of applause!
[AUDIENCE claps]
Ah! I'm totally nervous!
Don't you worry about a thing.
I'm here for you.
Shut up!
[MR. FUNAZU] I'd like to
sincerely thank the members
of the Board of Tourism
for putting on
this wonderful event
for us this evening.
Okay, students!
Like I always say,
make the day fun!
[AUDIENCE claps]
[taiko drums play]
[GROUP]
Ha!
[AUDIENCE claps]
It's your turn.
Good luck out there.
Thanks!
Okay, the next
number is called:
"The Blood-Soaked Santa"?
Oh, wow, I remember that story!
Oh, man, Christmastime
is almost upon us,
once again.
Hello there, Mr. Reindeer?
Why the heck do I have to
hand out presents tonight?
That's obviously Papa's job!
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I know it's hard to believe it,
but I couldn't make
a turn on an icy road,
and so we ended up crashing.
There's simply too much
snow in Manoyama.
But you can fly, can't you?
What were you doing
on the road, anyway?
And where on earth is Papa?
Well, you see...
Huh?
Santa, you're here!
What happened?
I thought for sure
you were dead!
I'm not dead!
I might have been soaked
in blood, but I'm not dead!
Those little punks
at Second Middle School
were spreading lies!
You lied! So did you!
That's why I'm
asking you, daughter.
Will you do this?
Will you take
my place this year?
I don't want to!
Kids these days are
all totally selfish.
[TAIRA] I want a brand
new combine harvester!
That won't fit in the chimney!
And I want my very own
house with a garden!
Go ask an oil baron!
[AUDIENCE laughs]
There are still so many to go!
Please! There used to be
way more kids than this.
It was a whole lot harder then!
Yay, declining birthrates!
--[AUDIENCE laughs]
--I can't take any more.
But I know I've got to try.
Everyone is out there
waiting to get their presents.
There's one for you!
And there you go!
[ACTOR 20A] I hope Santa
will get here soon!
I know, I can hardly wait!
[MAKI, SHIBUKAWA]
Ho, ho, ho!
Yay! Thanks, you rock, Santa!
Hooray! Thanks, Santa!
This is exactly
the one I wanted!
[SHIBUKAWA] The sun is
gonna be up really soon.
Give it up, we'll get the
others to them next year.
No, I can't.
Not when there are still
kids out there waiting.
I remember what
Papa used to say.
"No matter how difficult it
gets, it's never hard at all."
Now, after this,
I finally understand
what he meant.
[SHIBUKAWA]
What's that?
[MAKI]
It's pretty simple.
I'm the one who's getting
the real gift tonight.
You got a gift?
That's right!
Everyone's smiling faces!
[AUDIENCE]
Ahh!
We made that with our
class back in the day!
[AUDIENCE clapping]
[SHIBUKAWA]
Director.
[clapping continues]
Okay, guys. Let's do it.
Thanks so much, everyone!
[clapping continues]
[YOSHINO] That concludes
our Closing Ceremony.
Thanks for joining us tonight.
The year after next,
this place is scheduled
to be an empty lot.
So...
For that reason,
we, the Tourism Board,
would like to make a proposal.
This wonderful building
once housed a school
that helped children
grow and thrive.
That purpose may be over now,
but why don't we
give it a new one:
helping Manoyama
grow and thrive!
What if we revived the life
in these dear old halls
as a base for Manoyama culture?
I believe that we can do it!
A base for Manoyama culture.
That's a much better idea
than just demolishing it.
Everyone!
I'd now like to present
our official proposal.
[YOSHINO] The Manoyama Second
Middle School Opening Ceremony!
The heck?
When they'd do this?
Oh, they asked me
to rig that up for 'em.
My friends, starting today,
we'd like to make Second Middle
School a public facility,
open to everyone!
[AUDIENCE claps]
Not a bad idea.
[GROUP]
Cheers!
I haven't felt this way
for a long time!
I know! Reading the surveys,
lots of folks say
they'd like to use the school!
Past choir members want to form
a new mother's chorus!
So sweet!
[YOSHINO] By the way, Maki,
you did an amazing job!
Thanks, so did you!
Your speech was so passionate!
[chuckles]
Really? Thank you!
I guess your passionate
performance inspired me!
You're actually an impressively
driven person, Maki.
It's good to meet you!
Oh, stop it,
you're a total weirdo.
So, hey, I've been thinking.
I might like to start an acting
troupe there at the school.
Acting troupe?
If there's nothing to do,
it's up to us to create it!
That's right!
So what play
are you gonna do?
Well, I've been
thinking I'd like to try
adapting the Dragon Song
into a play.
[SHIORI]
No way, really?
Yeah! You guys said it
was hard to understand
with just the song alone.
So, I think we should
tell the whole story!
That's a great idea.
It'd be cool if we could combine
it with the Mizuchi Festival.
[SHIORI] I love the idea
of a play at the festival!
Let's do it!
And the theme is co-existing
with other cultures.
I can think of no better
setting than the festival
for keeping that story alive,
can you?
Then, at the very end,
Riichan can burst out
and sing the whole song!
I'm filled with
anticipation and trepidation.
Hey, it's okay! So am I!
But we'll work together
and make it happen.
What'll be the name
of the acting troupe?
Come on,
isn't it pretty obvious?
The Royal Chupakabura
Acting Troupe!
Hell, no! Not that!
Anything but that!
All right, sir, that's it.
We'll go ahead and
get started on the repairs,
like you requested.
Here's the thing, no one
remembers requesting it.
[MOVER 20B] The order
was placed by this person.
Who's Mita Kyuro?
Maybe "Santa Claus"?
[SANAE]
Are you kidding me?
Well, the request
wasn't made by us.
That may very well be true,
but we've already
been paid in full, so...
What?
[MINO] We have a benevolent
Secret Santa.
Yeah, and what a mystery.
I'm dying to know who it is.
No, it couldn't be.
[SANDAL] "The Oden Detective
part 2" is brilliant.
The part with the
trick that involves
the difference between
karashi and mustard
is pure genius.
Next time: "The Pixie
in the Town of Ice."