[USHIMATSU]
Attention, everyone!
I've just come up
with a new form
of Manoyama Wood Carving!
Feast your eyes on this baby!
It's made out of dried bonito!
The first edible carving
in the industry!
It makes a perfect
table decoration,
and it's sure to cause
a stir in the world
of wood-carving!
Except that's not wood
carving--it's fish-carving.
[USHIMATSU]
Semantics! Who cares?
[SANAE]
I can't do this anymore.
I shouldn't be involved
if I have no purpose
and I'm not putting
my heart into it.
And yet you assume
you're qualified to talk
about Manoyama Wood Carving?
What a joke.
Hey! What's wrong, Queen?
Have you been listening
to anything I've said?
Please give me another
chance to do this!
[SHIORI] Yoshino said she
really wants to take her time
and learn some more about
Manoyama Wood Carving
before forging ahead.
So our meeting
today is canceled.
Not sure about this whole
"study on our own" thing though.
[YOSHINO] This one's
even cooler than the one
at Sanae's place.
Do you know about when
this might've been carved?
Let's see, we had
the remodeling done
for our 25th anniversary,
so I guess it's been
about 20 years.
You don't have to tell
her everything she asks!
Oh, hey, Gen, you're there!
Listen, the queen wants to come
see your ranma , no photos.
She wants to inspect
it up close.
Also, if you know of
any other houses
that have ranma , we'd love...
[door opens]
[MAKI] We're all supposed
to study on our own today.
I'm gonna make lunch.
Want anything?
[SANAE]
No thanks.
I'm going out.
You're running away again,
just like you did
when you came here.
Leave me alone, would you?
[SHIORI sighs]
What'd I do?
I picked the most
boring book ever!
What a waste.
What are you studying,
Rii- chan ?
[RIRIKO]
Wood carvings around the world.
That one's actually
a little scary.
[RIRIKO]
That's why I like it.
[SHIORI laughs]
This takes me
back to high school.
Remember how we always
used to study together
for our big exams?
[RIRIKO]
Mm-hmm.
Don't you think you
should get ready now?
Probably, yeah.
Come on, man.
You can't skip this.
This is how I pay my respects.
[USHIMATSU]
I appreciate it, Gen.
[YOSHINO]
Thanks so much for your time!
How was that?
Was it helpful for you at all?
Sure!
Seeing a bunch of ranma up close
is a totally
different experience
from looking at pictures!
[USHIMATSU]
Hmm.
I suppose that makes sense.
All right!
On to the next one, then.
[MOTHER 5A]
C'mon, Hideo. Dinner's ready!
[HIDEO]
Okay, Mom!
[FATHER 5A]
That looks delicious!
[MOTHER 5A] Could you
hand me a plate, hon'?
[FATHER 5A]
Sure!
That you, Sanae?
Oh! Tatsuo.
I just came from a wake.
A customer passed who'd
been buying from us
since back when our
master ran the shop.
Mind if I join you for a sec?
No, not at all.
[TATSUO chuckles]
I recently discovered your blog.
What do ya call it,
"The Thrilling Adventures
of a Rural Web Designer"?
Is that right?
So you're saying you read it?
Uh... Should I not have?
I don't know.
I mean, no, I don't really care.
[SANAE]
When I came here, this station
was my first official
introduction to Manoyama.
[TATSUO] Yeah, I guess it was
the same way for me, too.
[SANAE] I never wrote
about it on my blog,
but I used to come to
this bench and sit here
for hours on end when
I was feeling down
just to think things over.
I'd remind myself again of
the reasons I moved here.
How I needed a change
of pace and all that.
But work was still rough,
and I was pretty lonely.
But when I was at the station,
I'd sit here and look
down the track,
and I'd think about
how it leads to Tokyo,
and the world,
and it made me feel
less alone somehow.
Who would've thought
in this world of
online connections
that I'd be more comforted
by a train track?
Yeah, no, I get it.
A train track represents
a physical connection.
The old fashioned
kind of connection
that we rarely get anymore
because we're all so
"plugged in."
Plus, I love all the stations
and how much history they have.
I just wish the trains would run
later, and more frequently.
Do you take trains very often?
I took one to the city for a
sculptor's guild meeting once.
Had a bit of a problem.
I was rushing to catch
the train home and I tripped,
and my shoes flew off.
But it was the last train,
so I jumped on, barefoot,
and left the shoes behind!
[chuckles]
Like Cinderella!
Yeah, I guess, if
Cinderella had hairy legs!
[SANAE chuckles]
Yoshino, I'm home.
Good! You're back!
Hey, do you want some of this?
It's just pizza toast
with some fried veggies.
Are you deliberately trying
to make me fat, or what?
Maki's in the bath right now,
but you can go next
if you want to.
Sure, thanks.
Okay, guys!
Today, we reconvene
to officially resume
our WCD Tourism Plan meetings!
Where's Sanae?
Oh...
Sanae still isn't feeling
quite like her usual self,
so she'll be out for
a little while longer.
Anyhoo!
I think it'd be cool
for us all to share
what we learned from
our self-directed
Manoyama Wood Carving studies!
I'll go!
Great!
Well, I already knew
that Manoyama Wood Carving
flourished due to so
many bushi gathering
in Monzenmachi,
so I decided to go further
and research why they
started carving ranma .
No way, I looked
into that, too!
The Buddhist statue-shop-sign-
ranma thing?
Right!
They started with
Buddhist statues,
then they began
creating shops signs
and when demand
for those died down,
they moved on to ranma .
They shifted with the trends,
and they were able
to survive as a result.
Interesting.
So maybe it's just that
traditional Japanese houses
are less popular than before,
which means that a new
era might be about to begin!
What it comes down
to is that we need
to try to anticipate
what the next era's
going to bring, right?
But while we're sitting
here thinking about it,
the number of people
considering becoming
a professional wood
carver is dropping fast.
Yes!
But I think I've come up
with a great idea!
We should make a massive
wood-carved building!
We can remodel
the Chupakabura Palace,
and use a bunch of
wood carving to turn it
into an amazing palace!
All that studying
led you to this solution?
Yep, it did!
We'll be just like Sky Tree,
and Ushiku Daibutsu in
Ibaraki, and the Eiffel Tower!
If you build it,
they will come, am I right?
I wonder if it's
really that easy.
No, it won't be easy at all.
That's why we'll have
to really take our time
and do it the right way--
completing it piece by piece.
I'm talking about
doing it old school;
spending hundreds of years
on a legacy landmark...
...like the Sagrada Familia!
It's called Sakura Pond Familia!
If we can get
some news coverage,
people from all over
the world will be eager
to come contribute carvings!
Manoyama Wood Carving
techniques will be passed down,
our tourism will boom,
and we'll create new jobs!
It's kills three birds
with one stone!
Where do you suggest
we get the money?
Well, I mean, we could
charge for admission
and sell some souvenirs, right?
If it was easy
to draw tourists,
we wouldn't have this problem!
Anyhow, the reason
The Sakurada Familia's
a success is because
it was designed
by the great architect, Vivaldi!
Except it's Sagrada,
not Sakurada.
And it was Gaudi,
not Vivaldi, so--
Well, why don't we
get someone famous
to help us out, too?
Fine, then, go find us
a bargain-rate Vivaldi!
No worries, right?
[TV 5A]
But that's not all!
On top of the tree pruner,
if you act now
you'll also get a hand-held saw,
plus pruning shears...
[SANAE]
Ugh!
I have to stop!
This is where I was before!
I have to at least handle
my own business!
[doorbell chimes]
[SANAE]
Coming!
Is it a bad time?
[ANGELICA]
Thank you for waiting.
[SANAE]
Hm?
[TATSUO] Sorry to drop
in on you like that.
But I was just kind
of anxious to show you
what I've been working on.
Be honest. What do you think?
They're really
unique, aren't they?
Yeah, I hope so.
I was inspired to make them
after we talked about Cinderella
back at the train station!
Truth be told,
I don't know all that much
about women's shoes, though.
[chuckles]
So I was hoping maybe you
could help produce them?
Don't you think it
might upset Kazushi?
I don't care if it does.
[TATSUO] The ranma that
Kazushi is working on right now
was originally a job
our master took on
before he died a year back.
Kazushi picked up
where he left off
and he's been trying
to complete it.
But that wake the other night,
it was for the customer
who ordered it,
so the now the
order is canceled.
But even so,
Kazushi keeps carving away.
He says he has to finish it.
That sounds about right.
He's just being stubborn.
Wood carving is our profession.
If you're not getting paid,
there's no point.
[music playing]
[YOSHINO] I guess this is all
easier said than done, huh?
[SHIORI]
C'mon, no worries, Yoshi!
Though, what Mr. Kadota
said was fair, actually.
Nobody is going to
invest in this as-is.
The quality of the
product doesn't matter
if the creator's unknown.
What matters is whether
or not they're famous.
Content's an afterthought.
That's how the world works.
Look, it's Sandal.
Huh?
[RIRIKO] Why don't we
ask Sandal for help?
Now that you mention it,
he might be great to talk to.
He's really well known
in this town.
But only as a super-freak.
Have you seen the paintings
on the walls at Angelica's?
Most people don't
know who he is,
but he's a star in some circles.
A vagabond artist.
His real name is Alexandre
Cena Davis Celibidache.
'Kinda name's that?
Why do you think
he lives in Manoyama?
[YOSHINO] I don't know,
but we have to talk to him!
He could end up being a really
important artist someday!
Uhh...
I hope Yoshi will be okay.
I'm more curious
about what Sandal did
to get in trouble
with the police.
'Cause he's really
a world-famous spy
wanted for questioning.
In a tumultuous fight
over classified documents
in the Kingdom of Chupakabura!
Hey, keep quiet about that!
[laughing]
I'm gonna go get Sanae.
I think she might be out.
She wasn't in her room earlier.
I don't get it.
It feels like she
might really be done
working with us.
Well, I don't know about that,
but why don't we just
let her be for now.
I know I've felt
that way before.
[YOSHINO]
I'm back!
I got Sandal to do
a drawing for us!
Oh, so he was released?
He wasn't arrested!
Turns out he
was just hitchhiking.
He seriously hitched
with the cops?
Yeah, then he wanted to
stay and have a cup of tea
at the station.
So he sketched it out
while we sipped on some!
Hurry up and show us.
[YOSHINO]
Are you ready for this?
Ta-da!
[SHIORI]
Wow.
[MAKI] People might
actually show up for that.
Right?
It's gonna work, for sure!
These are the members
of the Chamber of Commerce.
Let's start by looking for
some sponsors who live here!
Rii- chan , you'll be
in charge of direct mail.
All right.
I worked part-time
as a telemarketer.
Perfect!
In that case, you should
handle the phones.
Shiori and I can
split up the duty
of making cold calls
to people's houses.
Good luck, all!
[YOSHINO]
Let's go, team!
[GROUP]
Go!
Oh, hey, Queen!
Where're you off to today?
I'm gonna make some cold calls!
Wow, you're really
embracing this.
You're not the same girl
who tried to run away.
Ah! Man, I did, didn't I?
Had you really forgotten?
Well, I suppose being a hot mess
is kinda part of
your charm, though.
A what?
Like you're one to talk,
Mr. Former Prince
Now Bus Driver.
Okay, well,
that came out wrong,
'cause I meant it
as a compliment.
Yep, if I were to be
completely honest with you,
this former prince could
learn from the queen.
[door opens]
[YOSHINO]
I'm back!
[SANAE]
Hey! Let me get you some tea.
Thanks, that'd be great!
[sighs] So tired...
[SANAE] You've been
working your butt off.
Takamizawa said the
same thing this morning.
Thanks so much!
[gasps] Where'd those come from?
They're cute!
Tatsuo actually made them.
Did he, really?
Yeah, I guess that
is wood carving.
How cool that some people
use wood to carve shoes,
and others use it
to carve ranma .
I think I get it now.
Huh?
[YOSHINO] The thing you
said before about being
easily replaced.
I know what you were
trying to say now.
You think that plenty of people
could take your place here.
[YOSHINO] You know,
you're absolutely right.
I mean, for instance,
my job as queen
was supposed to be
filled by that actress,
Yoshino Tsubaki.
Remember all of that?
[SANAE laughs]
So you're saying even
the queen can be replaced.
Right.
I don't think there's
a job out there
that somebody else can't do.
Well, that's depressing.
Thank you for that.
No, it's not, though!
I'm sure the things I do as
queen are totally different
from what Yoshino Tsubaki
would have done
if she'd been here in my place.
But even if every job can
be done by someone else,
some results can
only be achieved
by certain people
because we're all unique.
I'm sure it was the same
with your job in Tokyo!
Maybe it seemed the
same no matter who did it.
But if you looked closer,
I'm sure you'd find
that there was at least
some small part of you
hidden in that work.
Who can say, really?
Over that whole time, though,
no one praised me for a
job well done, not once.
[YOSHINO]
That's okay!
Some people will
notice our hard work,
and some people never will.
Some people might
love what we've done,
and some might reject it because
they're coming
at it differently.
All of that is good because our
differences make us stronger,
and when we come together,
then we can create
something new.
Ugh! I'm not saying it right,
but I think we're all here
because our quirks
complement each other
and I believe we can
accomplish great things!
Thanks, Yoshi.
[phone ringing]
Oh, the owner of the
company I just talked to!
Hi, you've reached the queen!
Oh, no problem at all!
Yes, that'll work fine!
Thanks so much!
Yes!
Sanae!
[SANAE]
This is an impressive proposal.
And an ambitiously
absurd concept.
I see Yoshino's work here.
But I think it might be really
tough to actually get it done.
That's why your Minister
of IT has come up
with a couple of practical
plans to try to push it through.
See?
First, there's the
money problem.
We'll continue
our current methods
of searching for sponsors,
plus add crowdfunding.
I've never heard
of "crowdfunding."
It's the latest way to raise
funds for certain projects
and it seems pretty
popular and effective.
Right.
You use the internet
to gather supporters
and invite them to contribute.
It's being utilized
all over the world.
We also need to consider
where to build it.
I know the current plan is
to build where the palace is
but I'd like to
propose another spot.
I think we should
use the train station.
Really? Why is that?
A station's a door to a city.
It's also already a landmark
for the people of Manoyama.
They greet and say goodbye
and stories are born there.
We can add color to those
stories with wood carvings.
And check it out.
You see?
He's drawn the station.
Doesn't it seem a little crazy
to suddenly rebuild the station?
True.
That's why, to start off,
we're going to cover the
waiting room with ranma .
And it's gonna be
just like the ceiling
of the Sistine Chapel.
[GROUP]
Oh.
[SANAE]
And I know exactly which piece
we should put up first.
[SANAE]
You were absolutely right.
You had me pegged.
I ran away from Tokyo
without thinking about
what it all meant.
But the place I ran to,
this town,
gave me the chance
to find that meaning
within myself.
[KAZUSHI] Did you come
over here just to tell me that?
No, but we came here to
discuss something with you.
Isn't it true that the person
who ordered that ranma
cancelled the order?
What are you trying to say?
We actually have a proposal.
A way to ensure that
wood-carving remains here
for centuries without
compromising your ideals.
And a way for
Manoyama Wood Carving
to become known
throughout the whole world.
It'll also affect the
future carving pupils here.
You're carving from
a zelkova tree, right?
Judging by the ranma 's size,
I'd guess the tree was
150 to 200 years old!
We're asking.
Please help us keep
pursuing the meaning
that we've found here!
This is it! This is exactly
what I was looking for!
All right!
Well, I guess we're all done!
Nope, this is
just the beginning!
[SANAE] We'll spend the next
hundred years working on it,
but this is the first step.
Speaking of steps,
I'm looking forward
to working with you
on my wooden shoes.
Leave it to me!
I've been giving it whole
lot of thought lately,
and I wonder where else
can we take this idea.
The key is to infuse
everyday items
with Manoyama Wood Carving.
You know, Kazushi,
today's a big day for you,
and it really is okay
to smile about it.
Uh... Yeah. It's not bad.
Wow, that's my
first praise ever.
Huh?! What he said?
It was high praise from him.
We've really done it!
We've taken the first step
for Sakura Pond Familia.
Kinda makes you wish
we could live long enough
to see it finished.
I get that.
It is kinda sad.
But our kids and
grandkids will love it!
Yeah.
--Oh!
--Ahh!
--[WOMAN 5B] How lovely!
--[WOMAN 5C] Well, look at that!
[SANDAL]
Hello!
I'm the walking Sandal!
And my hobby is gardening.
Next time:
"The Rural Masquerade."