[IWASHITA]
Three Sacred Treasures, huh?
[YOSHINO]
Right!
The Staff, the Hanging Drum,
and the Golden Dragon.
We need to revive the festival.
We have to have
the treasures to do that.
Any idea where they could be?
It's fifty years
since the last festival.
The priest passed away
a long time ago,
and even the shrine
itself is gone.
Our work is cut
out for us, huh?
Tell me! Did your
grandma know anything?
Unfortunately not.
Oh, no!
My grandma and grandpa
said that they don't
remember anything about
the festival treasures either.
I guess we'll make our own.
It's not DIY.
[NOGE] I would bet the
professor might know.
What professor?
We get a lot
of orders from him.
I heard he used to teach
at some college.
Let's see.
Ah, here we go.
He's the one who
wrote this book.
"Cultural Anthropology."
Oh!
This was once my textbook
for a college course.
What a small world.
Wow, and he lives in Manoyama?
He lives by himself
in Warabiya Village
out in the mountains.
But, he's quite an
eccentric old man.
I'm intrigued.
Should we go?
Warabiya is pretty deep in
the mountains, you know.
[YOSHINO]
It's my first time out this far.
It must be hard living
in a place like this.
Yeah, makes you wonder
where they go shopping.
[YOSHINO]
Excuse me! Mr. Suzuhara?
Are you at home, sir?
Maybe he's out.
[GROUP gasps]
That was scary.
[SUZUHARA]
Well, well, look at that.
Five sneaky tanukis at my door.
Can I help you?
Just to be clear,
did he call us tanukis?
[MAKI]
Yes. Yes, he did.
[SHIORI] I have a feeling
he might know a lot
about the past, though.
Cultural anthropology.
It involves taking up residence
in the region being researched,
and observing its
culture and society
over a long period of time.
[SUZUHARA]
Exactly.
Rather than tracing
back to the past,
this field focuses solely
on knowing the present.
Anybody care for a drink?
[MAKI]
We're all fine, thanks, though.
That was a joke.
This stuff would be
wasted on tanukis.
I'm hosting the queen
and her ministers, am I?
Oh, you've heard of us, then?
[SUZUHARA] I saw you on
"Moving Mountains."
Playing at your little
rural revival games.
What do you mean by "games"?
We take our work very seriously!
Hey, it's okay, Shiori.
[SUZUHARA] And you're here
to ask about the festival
that ended fifty years ago, huh?
Yes, sir!
The five of us are committed
to trying to bring it back!
That's interesting.
Unfortunately, I only moved to
Manoyama twenty years ago.
What are you aiming
to accomplish
by reviving it, anyhow?
[YOSHINO]
Uhh...
Remember, it didn't
end on its own.
The fact it ended means
no one cared about it.
Don't you agree?
No, I actually don't.
I think the people
really need it.
They need a place to return to.
A place to gather.
C'mon, Let's go.
It seems to me like this
professor doesn't know anything.
[SUZUHARA]
I never said I didn't know.
I've heard rumors in the
village, over the years.
Apparently, one of
the treasures is held
in the storehouse of a
certain traditional home.
[MAKI] If he knew,
he should've just told us
from the start!
I really can't stand
people like that.
He reminds me of someone.
What're we gonna do?
There are so many
storehouses around here.
We're just gonna
have to check at each one.
[SANAE]
Hm?
[YOSHINO]
Sanae!
[SUZUHARA] I think I'll play a
little game with those tanukis.
[GROUP chattering]
Hey! Isn't that Takamizawa?
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Yeah.
I've tried talking to my company
about it several times!
[SHIGE] You do understand
what you're doing,
taking away our
freedom like this?
[GORO] And what about those
of us that live alone, hm?
I had thought you understood
and were on our side
about this, Takamizawa.
I'm disappointed.
[TAKAMIZAWA] Come on,
please don't say that, Kiyo!
I wonder what's up.
From what I've heard, this area
is about to be removed from
the current bus route.
People are upset.
[YOSHINO]
Oh, wow.
[MASA]
Please forgive the mess.
I haven't given the storehouse
a proper cleaning for years!
Oh, and if you see
any naughty mags,
just pretend you didn't!
[laughs]
Masa, what is that? A tablet?
Oh, this thing?
Someone from the
city offices left it here
a little while back.
I have no clue
how to use it,
but it's pretty helpful for
night time bathroom trips.
Oops! The batteries!
[SANAE yelps]
Someone just touched my butt!
[RIRIKO]
It wasn't me.
[MASA]
Me neither!
[MAKI]
Hide, hello sir.
[SHIORI] Thanks so much
for letting us look through
your storehouse!
Sure thing. Did you
find what you needed?
[SHIORI]
I'm afraid not.
That's too bad.
I'm sorry that I
couldn't be more help.
Not at all! We appreciate it!
Are you fixing
one of your tools?
You still enjoy work, don't you?
Oh, no, I've been retired
for quite some time now.
I'm just keeping up
the routine at this point.
It can be a hard habit
to break, you know.
I made my living
this way for decades.
Of course, makes sense!
[timer beeping]
[HIDE]
Oh, good!
It's time for lunch!
So, you use the...?
It's very useful.
It works as a timer,
and as a weight!
Yep, they're useful, all right!
[door opens]
[YOSHINO]
I'm a hungry girl!
Oh, hey, Takamizawa!
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Hey!
[ERIKA] Lunch A: Tonkatsu.
Lunch B: Hot Somen.
--[YOSHINO] I'll go with "A."
--[MAKI] Same here.
I'll take "B," please.
[SANAE]
"B" for me, too.
--Curry.
--'Kay.
[sighs]
[YOSHINO]
Takamizawa!
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Huh?
We saw you the other day.
That looked rough.
Oh, yeah, that's okay.
There's nothing I can
do about it, anyway.
I understand.
But what happens if those stops
are taken off the route?
I think in cases like this
they usually replace it
with a subsidized
community bus.
So things won't actually
change much, then?
[TAKAMIZAWA] Well, the local
government isn't exactly rich.
Running just one bus for a year
costs over ten million yen.
That much?
And we only get
about ten riders a day
from Warabiya Village.
Not that they don't matter,
because they do, but
the buses aren't
the only problem, here.
I mean, there's no hope
of the town growing
at this point.
They just have to make
sure to live within their means
from here on out.
That sounds so harsh.
You guys only talk
about boring stuff.
That's why I want to get
out of this stupid little town.
[USHIMATSU coughing]
Old ass!
[coughing]
[sighs] Damn, I thought
I might die, there.
So. What do you
want with me, anyway?
[CHITOSE]
You just keep hanging on, huh?
[USHIMATSU]
You show up out of nowhere
and greet me like that?
[CHITOSE yells]
I won't be back!
Hurry up and die, already!
[USHIMATSU]
What the hell?
[GORO] This bus thing's
a total catastrophe.
If I start using taxis now,
I'm going to be broke
in no time.
We'll worry about that later.
Those of us who can
drive will be flexible
and help each other out.
[GORO] Masa, you can
barely see at night!
You shouldn't be driving at all!
I still seem to have a
sixth sense for butts, though!
[GROUP laughs]
They were standing
around by the door,
so I brought them in.
Is that okay, Professor?
Of course.
Everyone, the queen is here.
Thanks very much.
It's nice to meet you all.
Ah! I saw you on TV once!
That other girl's from
The Oden Detective !
Kids these days
are remarkable.
The one with the glasses
is my type o' lady.
Talk about a caboose.
It was you, old bastard.
So, what brings
you all here today?
Well, I don't look the part,
but I am the queen,
so I thought I should
learn more about
how different people live here.
[SUZUHARA]
Hmm. Interesting.
As I assume
you're well aware,
the bus will stop
coming around here
before much longer.
We want to stop
that from happening.
What do you think?
We want to hear young
people's thoughts.
You first, Ms. Koharu.
Uh... Oh, umm...
If they drive slow and
focus on efficiency--
That's an "F."
A truly pointless effort.
Next, Ms. Shinomiya.
Increase fares so that
they don't operate at a loss,
I guess?
[SUZUHARA]
Fail.
Any and all fare changes require
approval from the government.
[SUZUHARA]
Next, Ms. Midorikawa.
Make the buses smaller.
[SUZUHARA]
That's a C minus.
We still can't reduce
people's salaries.
So what do we do, Ms. Oribe?
Wait until self-driving cars
have finally become popular.
That's an "F."
We obviously won't be
alive when that happens.
Last one. Ms. Kozuki.
This affects the whole country.
The decreasing population
problem isn't limited
to our town.
With that in mind,
towns with dwindling populations
should try to move their
citizens to more central areas.
Compact communities can be
reconstructed in urban zones.
If you do that, I believe
the transportation problem
should be resolved.
Big fail.
These people worked hard
up until their retirement,
and paid their taxes.
This is their rightful home.
They should be able to live
here as long as they want.
[MASA]
That's right, we should.
[KIYO] I don't want
to move at this age.
Ms. Kozuki.
When you break up an older
community such as ours,
what you're really
doing is breaking up
that region's culture.
[SANAE]
Oh...
Your urban life
left you ignorant
of the situation in the country.
I say that even though
I am from Tokyo, myself.
[SANAE]
Really?
I moved here from the city, too.
I had no direct
connection to Manoyama.
All right,
just one more question.
What was it that made
you choose to come here?
[SANAE]
Huh?
[SUZUHARA] On that TV program,
it seemed a little like
you didn't much
care where you went.
That's not really--
[SUZUHARA]
Don't worry. It's fine.
Believe me, I didn't have
any special feelings
for this place, either.
However, over the years,
I've put down roots here.
[SUZUHARA] By the way, how's
your treasure hunt coming along?
Going okay.
We've been trying to hit up
every place with a storehouse,
but there sure are a lot of 'em.
Unless we find a way
to get help from others,
there'll be no end.
That's the kind of thing
your generation is good at.
Ms. Kozuki.
Yes?
[SUZUHARA]
What are you the minister of?
Time you made use
of your weapons.
That was a complete
waste of a trip.
Except, what the professor
said was totally true.
I'm the queen here now,
but I know next to nothing
about this town.
Make use of my weapons, huh?
Hey, what's the deal
with those tablets
that the city workers
left with some of them?
What was that?
Oh, the municipal
government recently
handed those out
to seniors living alone.
The idea was that they
could get health checkups
while they were at home.
I'm not sure they're actually
being used that way, though.
But that means the
groundwork is already there.
Ooh! Do you have an idea?
Don't you think
a town where the seniors
are internet savvy
could be a cool thing?
Then we'd be able to use
the internet to ask them
about the lost festival
treasures, too!
--[SHIORI] Sounds great!
--[YOSHINO] Yeah!
We can call it:
"The Plan to Teach
Manoyaman Seniors
Social Media and Gather the
Missing Festival Treasures"!
Concise.
We'll call it the
Mano-S plan for short!
[KIYO] Oh, no!
I touched the wrong thing again.
[SANAE] This is where you
switch to hiragana.
And this is where
you convert it to kanji!
Then you just tap
right here, see?
Oh!
That's actually
pretty easy, isn't it?
So, this one is for pictures?
Yeah, that's right!
And this is for video.
[RIRIKO] If you press here,
you can go back.
[KIYO]
Oh, you're right!
Thanks, young lady!
I want to know
more about butts.
[TABLET]
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
Masa, come on,
what are you doing?
You got butts in there?
[TABLET] I don't think I'm ready
for that kind of relationship.
[MAKI]
Oh, my god.
[SHIORI]
It reads like this, see?
[tablet chimes]
Okay! Now you're registered!
You can send each other
messages whenever you want!
Wow.
Learning from a pretty young
lady sure did make this easier!
[laughs]
Everyone!
If you've got any friends that
couldn't make it here today,
please ask them about
the festival treasures
if you would!
[GROUP]
Okay!
[OLDER MAN 17A]
All right!
Did you get a shot of that one?
[OLDER MAN 17B]
Yep, it's perfect!
You're in a little bit
a trouble, then, aren't cha?
[OLDER MAN 17D]
I don't know who this guy is,
but he's surprisingly good!
Now Bishop to King,
and that's checkmate.
Adios, Lucia!
I hope you find the matsudodon!
Gracias, amiga!
See you again!
That's so cool!
You became really good
friends with the Cryptids,
huh, Riichan?
Manoyama's network
keeps getting bigger and bigger!
You know, seniors generally
tend to stick together, too.
But by reinforcing their
communication via the web,
the seniors will
feel less isolated!
The Mano-S Plan
has some unexpected benefits!
And before long, the buses
will all be driving themselves.
[SANAE] The professor said it'll
take another couple decades,
but it's possible now,
technologically speaking.
If it's a legal issue,
they could make Manoyama
an exception, right?
[SHIORI] That would solve
the problem for people
who shouldn't be driving!
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Thanks.
Oh. Lost your appetite?
[TAKAMIZAWA]
I just feel kinda full.
Once the self-driving
cars make it here,
you'll be out of a job, huh?
Will not! What do you know
about it, anyway, little girl?
Buses are not that simple!
They aren't the same
as a car at all!
Some things just require
a human touch.
What are you talking about?
Your whole life's on rails!
You go round and around the
same route every single day!
No, buses don't go
on rails, you fool!
They move around freely,
like me, so there!
[ERIKA]
Why are you so pissed, loser?
The loser here is you!
Go, run on home,
Tacrappyzawa!
Shut up, flat-chest!
That's it, you're
banned from now on!
[TAKAMIZAWA]
Fine!
I have a feeling we
might've touched a sore spot
for Takamizawa.
Yeah, I think we did.
Hello, hello. I'm Onono Komachi.
--[MASA] I got it!
--[KIYO] Got it!
Turning your voice into writing.
It seems like magic!
And to think our generation
used rotary phones!
Now if you want to,
you can have your
community meet-ups
without ever leaving home!
[SHIGE] Thank you all so
much for your help with this!
[GORO]
Oh, yes, many thanks!
No, it's our pleasure!
It sure would be nice to
see the other person's face
while we talk.
Don't lie.
What you actually want
to see is their butts.
Damn straight!
[laughing]
See their face...
[USHIMATSU]
That was it! [chuckles]
[SHIORI]
Mr. Kadota!
[YOSHINO] You were released
from the hospital?
That's right, I'm back!
[laughing]
Oh, Minister of IT.
I heard you're treasure hunting
on the Internet.
Yes, we are,
but we also want more active
participation from seniors,
so we're thinking of making an
informational web series.
Sounds like fun.
You can use my
place if you want.
I've got a camera.
Really, Gen? Thank you!
That would be so perfect!
Hello, everyone!
Thanks for joining!
This is the new
Manoyama Channel,
the source for all
your local info!
For our viewers at home,
if you connect,
you'll show up
on a little screen,
so don't be afraid to
join in the conversation!
That's right, don't be shy!
[MASA]
Hey, can you see me?
Oh, we've already got one!
Hello, Masa. We can see you.
Looking sexy, as always, Sanae!
Masa! Come on, now!
You dirty old pervert.
That's me!
Oh, that's right! Hey, Gen?
How'd the Mahjong end up?
You won't believe it.
Ushimatsu ended up taking it
all his very first time back!
[MASA]
What? That crazy bum!
What the heck are they doing?
It doesn't matter; it's okay.
Yeah, it's not like we're trying
to get the whole world
to watch or anything.
It's just a community
for the people
of Manoyama to come together.
[SANAE] This afternoon,
we'll be broadcasting live
from Michiyo's house.
[GEN] Feel free to use your time
however you want, Michiyo!
[SANAE]
Michiyo?
[YOSHINO]
Huh?
[SANAE] Uh-oh, looks like she
hasn't noticed yet.
[MAKI, SHIORI, YOSHINO]
What is happening?
[NOGE] Those seniors
are surprisingly active.
You mean the
Manoyama Channel thing?
Yeah, check this guy out.
I make cabinets just for fun.
And I'm better at it
than these young kids.
He makes cabinets for fun.
Man, I feel lazy.
And look, there's a
bulletin board here, too.
There's this one old guy
who blew my mind
with how much he
knows about sixties jazz!
I can't believe I found someone
to talk about that with
in Manoyama!
So you've been
going to visit him lately?
Yeah, it's cool!
He lives way out
in the mountains,
so we can play records
as loud as we want
and no one complains.
And he's got this
super cool old amp!
This town's not bad!
Who woulda thought?
Huh.
That's crazy.
These old guys have gotten
pretty good with the web.
How's the group chat going?
[MAKI]
So far, so good.
Great! I bet we'll
learn something about
the festival treasures soon.
Is there anything new
in the questions section?
Well, we seem to be
getting the same question
over and over, actually.
I wonder why.
Those are some dirty old guys!
So, what about you?
[RIRIKO] People aren't getting
along very well on the boards.
Huh?
[SANAE] Maybe we should have
made them use their real names.
And it seems like more of them
are becoming shut-ins now.
[SANAE]
Huh?
Some of them are
commenting all day long.
Whoa, seriously?
I guess it's better than
having nothing to do, right?
Let's just keep an eye on them.
Where's Yoshino?
The professor called her,
so she went over to see him.
The professor?
--Whoa.
--What is it?
A fight is breaking out.
[SANAE] "I'm coming over
to kick your ass, Goro."
[SANAE] Hm?!
Wait, this is an actual threat!
Who the hell wrote that?
We'd better get over
to Goro's place right now!
[SHIGE]
You fat young punk!
I should have known it
was you who threatened me!
You're imagining things!
Where's your proof,
you skinny old corpse?
Would you stop it, you two?
You're both well over
eighty years old!
[SANAE]
What's going on?
[SHIGE] This guy is constantly
making fun of me!
Making sneaky remarks online!
[GORO]
I'd say it to your face!
When would I have taken
that picture, anyway?
[RIRIKO] "Look at Shige's
tiny little cucumbers!
They're cracking me up!"
[SHIORI]
Huh?
Okay, okay, we got it!
Now let's calm down, please!
We're going to start
making everyone
use their real names
from now on.
[YOSHINO]
Are you serious?
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
I'll head right back.
Thanks to you
and your friends,
my friends and I have
actually learned quite a bit.
Thank you for that.
Well, looks like we've
created some problems, too.
At the dawn of
the internet, it was different.
People had to
register to use it,
so they were more courteous.
Then, screen names
were introduced,
encouraging lawlessness.
Next came flat-rate
plans creating shut-ins.
[chuckles]
History has a way of
repeating itself, huh?
I don't know that it's
anything to laugh about.
And remember, you were the
one who encouraged Sanae
to do this in the first place!
[SUZUHARA] Well, I
suppose the time is right.
Ms. Koharu.
I'm terribly sorry,
but I'm going to have
to take you hostage.
What, now?
[SHIORI]
Yoshi sure is late tonight.
She said she'd be
right back, didn't she?
She did. I wonder
if something happened.
--[RIRIKO gasps]
--What is it this time?
The professor's house.
[SUZUHARA] We, the people
of Warabiya village,
wish to express our
opposition to the removal
of our bus route,
as well our deep
disillusionment and rage.
People are the
foundation of the state.
If you deem it necessary
to forsake us,
then we will be forced
to do the same to you.
In light of that,
we hereby withdraw
from the Kingdom of Chupakabura!
What?!
They're withdrawing
from the Kingdom?
But not from Manoyama?
For real,
what is he talking about?
Hey, look over there!
It's Yoshi!
[MAKI] Girl, what is
going on with you?
[SENIORS]
Hey hey, ho! Hey, ho!
Ho.
[SANDAL] My cousin wouldn't
listen to his dad, my uncle,
for five whole years
after my uncle forgot
to erase his browsing history.
Next time:
"Minerva's Saké Saucer."