[HALLEY] Just as the name
"Mage Corps Battle" implies,
one class will face
the other in a mock battle.
Your professor will
be your commander,
and you will obey his orders.
Every spell will be considered
military-grade magic,
so those of you
we judge to be "dead"
must leave the battlefield.
The key to winning will
be how the commanders
deploy their forces
and the tactics employed
once combat begins.
You have three hours to fight.
If you can capture the
enemy base, your team wins.
You can also win by defeating
the enemy commander.
[clapping]
Wow, Herbs, you took
more time to explain
this fake war than it
would to fight a real one.
Good job. [chuckles]
This is a noble
site of learning
and you're using its students
to duel over a girl.
Have you no shame, sir?
Mr. Leos!
You better win this.
It's high time someone
knocks the smirk
off Glenn Radars's face!
As you wish.
Oh, Sistine.
Don't give me a moment's thought
when you're out there.
I want you to fight
as hard as you can.
[GIRLS gasp]
Because no matter what
happens on that field,
I will overcome it
and win your heart.
Aren't you sweet.
All right, useless maggots!
Win this battle
for your professor
so he can marry into money!
[STUDENTS] Why should we help
you get the girl and get rich?!
[SISTINE sighs]
So, be honest, now.
Are you really gonna marry
whomever wins this fight?
What? Marry?
Of course I'm not!
There're so many things
I wanna do in life
before I settle down!
They're the ones
getting carried away
with this magic duel thing.
[SISTINE] What if Professor
Radars does want to beat Leos,
so he can, well, y'know.
[GLENN (DREAM) yells]
[LEOS (DREAM) grunts]
[GLENN (DREAM) chuckles]
[SISTINE yells]
No! Why am I even
thinking about that?
No way could I
marry the professor!
She's acting weird, turning red.
Sistine's irritable
and yelling at everyone,
panting and all sweaty.
She sick?
In a way, I suppose so.
We should probably
take her to a doctor.
Not sick-sick,
and certainly nothing
that a doctor can cure.
All right!
The Mage Corps Battle between
class two and class four
starts right now!
[gong rings]
Thunder sprites shock!
Pay heed, great wind!
White winter!
[yelling]
Those were direct
hits on Ken and Chris
from class two!
Both guys are
outta the game now!
So far it's been no
surprise that the Academy's
famed class four
has shown magic power
far beyond class two.
They've even begun executing
three-man cell formations,
a decisive tactic
in mage combat!
Now, let's talk
modern mage combat.
More precisely,
how to succeed at it.
Now pay attention
to what I draw.
Left front squad
is your attack team,
right front circle
is defensive cover,
and the rear?
A supportive mage
position which provides
combat supply needs
to both forward units.
So we call this simple
formation "the three-man cell,"
and it's the most
successful tactic
in modern mage combat.
But if each mage is
specialized and focused
on one role,
then that would give them
a huge advantage against
massed enemy attacks.
Is that what you're saying?
[GLENN]
Nailed it, Gibster.
And each mage's life depends
on his comrade's actions.
You can be the best
mage in the world,
but if you've got a big ego,
and suck at teamwork,
you'll just end up putting
everyone's life in danger.
When you're on a
mage's battlefield,
there's no room for heroes.
That's the real lesson today.
Radars is sending
twelve to the central plain,
eight to the forest, one uphill.
Okay.
I'm sure three-man cells
would be too difficult
for his class.
This appears to be turning
into a much easier campaign
than I thought it'd be.
[ARS]
Professor Leos is making moves!
He's deploying more
troops than class two
to each area!
How will Professor
Radars respond?
[PROFESSOR 11A]
This won't take long.
The combination of
Professor Leos's command skill
and the movements of
class four are impressive.
In comparison,
the command of class two
is disorganized.
I suppose Professor
Radars is not
well-versed in
mage combat tactics.
[HALLEY] Professor Kleitos
is the top military
magic researcher.
Each of his class four
students is more skilled
than their class
two counterparts.
It's easy to think
he's got this in the bag.
Until you remember
who he's up against.
[ARS] Both armies are
trading blows at close range!
Thunder sprites, electric shock!
Pay heed, great wind!
[STUDENT 11C]
White winter storm, pay heed!
Wall of wind!
--[BIX] Wall of great wind!
--[KY] W-W-W-Wall of wind!
[ARS] Class two's putting
up a fight, folks!
They've stopped 'em
in their tracks!
What the hell's happening?
I thought we outpowered
them in combat strength!
No surprise.
You say on the battlefield,
there's no place for heroes.
So I take it you want us
to put our egos aside
and form the three-man cell?
What?
No way are you boners
ready for the three-man cell.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[GLENN]
Not only is it a pro tactic,
mastering it takes tons of
time that we don't have.
So what's our
strategy gonna be?
Calm down. I got a plan.
Thunder sprites shock!
[GIBUL]
Wall of great wind!
No way!
Those are two-man cells?
A smart move.
The two-man cell
is not as powerful
as a three-man cell,
but they're easy to
teach in a short time,
and to master.
Oh, please!
It's nothing more than a cheat,
and it smears the proud
history of the Academy!
Radars should be ashamed!
[HALLEY] No, he'll do
whatever it takes to win.
That's the kind of mage
Glenn Radars is.
[LEOS chuckles]
My goodness.
So that's your big plan?
Hit hard and then
retreat up to the hills
to assume sniping positions?
Rito? I need an update.
[RITO]
Things are not good!
Thunder sprites electric, shock!
There's still one left,
but she's a monster!
We don't have the
firepower to stop her!
[STUDENTS whimpering]
So some of your students
actually have talent.
Impressive, Radars,
but too late.
All troops to the forest.
We'll finish them off
with one large strike.
Switch to Woodland tactics, now.
[RUKIA]
Professor, we got company!
[GLENN laughing]
Behold, class four bitches!
The enemy general,
the great Glenn Radars,
stands before you!
If you think you can
best me in single combat,
let's get it on!
[laughing]
Woohoo!
Oh, wow!
Commander Radars
just moved himself
to the front lines!
Hey!
C'mon, let's get him!
[STUDENT 11F] If we take down
their commander, we win!
Thunder sprites electric shock!
[GLENN laughing]
[STUDENTS yell]
[GLENN]
Gotcha!
[STUDENTS yell]
What is this stuff?
No! Retreat! Retreat!
[STUDENTS yelling]
[GLENN laughs]
[GLENN]
I love guerrilla warfare!
It's gurrr-reat!
[laughing]
Hey, what are you doing
out here all by yourself?
Apparently watching
our illustrious "commander"
gloat over his dirty tricks.
Rukia, come in.
How do you read?
[GLENN]
Nothing that's not 18 and up.
[LEOS]
Professor Radars.
You set booby traps
before the battle started,
didn't you?
No way.
I think your boys just
got caught in some
eco tourism hipster
obstacle course, that's all.
[laughing]
Thunder sprites, shock!
[STUDENT 11G yelling]
Who wants some?
[STUDENT 11G yells]
Leave us alone!
[SISTINE panting]
That jerk.
He wants to win so badly
he's using booby traps?
[GLENN laughing]
My fake fiancé is
the biggest idiot ever.
Um, Sistine...
All right!
Counter-attack with
everything you've got!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Now! Don't let
them break through!
Thunder sprites electric shock!
Wall of Great Wind!
[gong rings]
All right! Time!
No clear winner
after three hours.
I declare the mock
mage battle a draw!
You're done!
I'm so beat.
All that for just a draw? C'mon!
[GLENN]
You all did great out there.
Holding your own
against a knob-job
like Leos ain't easy.
[STUDENTS chuckle]
But Professor,
what happens now?
Hold on.
How are we going
to know who Sistine's
going to marry meow?
Eh. No big.
[LEOS] What the hell was
that pathetic performance?!
If you had followed my orders,
we clearly would have won
and Sistine would be my wife.
That dude's a
selfish creeper, huh?
Hold on.
You're not being fair, here.
A good general never blames
his men for his failure.
I don't care!
Learn to keep your
opinions to yourself!
You know, we've both
had a long day.
Why don't we go--
[LEOS] Glenn Radars,
our duel remains unsettled.
I want a re-match.
And this time, I'm the one
issuing the challenge!
Really? You still haven't
given up on white cat?
Of course not.
The issue's not settled until
she gives up her studies,
and agrees to become my bride.
Hoo boy.
All right, fine.
I haven't given up on my dream
of marrying into money, either.
[SISTINE]
Knock it off! Both of you!
I'm sick of you
fighting over me!
It's so offensive!
Almost as offensive
as your dueling tactics!
They're just cowardly!
What makes you think
I'd marry someone
who doesn't fight honor--
Round two, tomorrow, let's go.
Meet in the Academy's back yard.
Mano-y-mano.
You sure about this?
If I win, I never have
to work again, ever.
Bet your pompous ass
I'm sure about thi--
So selfish.
I hate you.
[crying]
Sistine, wait!
Well! With that, we conclude
today's dramatic mage
combat war games.
Now, get lost!
[SISTINE]
What is wrong with him?
"Never having to work again"!
All he sees when he looks
at me is my family's money!
Sisti, calm down.
What?
We've gotten to know
him pretty well by now.
He cares about a lot more
than just making money.
Then why bother
challenging Leos to a duel?
I can't believe
you're still focusing
on that ridiculous fantasy.
[RUMIA] Well, maybe he
just got carried away.
Listen. I'm sure there's
a deeper reason for it.
He's too lazy to be
the duel fighting type.
You know, you could always
try talking to him.
C'mon, just ask him!
It can't hurt.
You can't just
hate Professor Radars
without knowing if it's
for the right reason.
Not to mention, maybe once
you do clear the air,
you guys can go back
to getting along
like you used to!
I guess.
Great!
You're right, thank you!
[RUMIA giggles]
[RUMIA] I need to talk
to the professor, too.
About the creepy feeling I got
when I was around Mr. Leos.
What was that all about, anyway?
[BERNARD] Well, boys,
this is a textbook case
if I've ever seen one.
[BERNARD] Another gruesome death
for an Angel's Dust addict.
You won't find a more
pathetic end than this.
I've heard the rumors
for a while now,
but I didn't expect
it to be this bad.
It is.
This makes five cases.
It's pretty clear to me:
This drug's spreading
a lot farther and faster
than we ever thought.
[ALBERT]
Angel's Dust.
What the hell's going on?
[LEOS]
Curse that Glenn Radars!
He is such a thorn in my side!
That's just the
kind of man he is.
But take solace in the
fact that he's nowhere near
your skills as a mage.
Glenn is the type,
who even if fated to lose
99 out of a hundred battles,
would pull out that one victory
in the very first round.
If I didn't know
you any better,
I'd say you admire Mr. Radars.
If I didn't, there'd be no
point to our roundabout methods.
Well, it doesn't matter
what you see in him.
He's still hardly
a match for me.
And after tomorrow,
Sistine will be all mine.
And once our
nuptials are official,
her family's fall will begin.
The Kleitos line
will gain control
over her detestable branch.
And my claim to sitting at
the head of the entire family
will at last be secure.
[JATICE laughs]
[GLENN sighs]
What a day.
[GLENN] At least it'll
be all over tomorrow.
I apologize, Leos.
I don't care how
much more you know
about magic than me.
I'm not losing to some
monocled douche
who does nothing but research.
It's too bad, though.
Whole experience leaves
such a bitter taste
in my mouth.
I'm well aware that I've
done wrong by white cat,
but it's all for the best.
Right, Sara?
[SISTINE]
It's not for the best!
[gasps] White cat?!
What's "you've done wrong
by white cat" mean?
Also, who's Sara?
I wanna know the truth.
Why'd you challenge
Leos to that duel?
Not this again.
I've told you over and over!
So I can marry into money!
If there's an opportunity
to never work
another day in my life,
I'm gonna take it.
Also, you remind me of Sara.
[GLENN]
A long, long time ago,
there lived a foolish young man.
This guy was obsessed with
becoming a Mage of Justice.
So he put everything
he had into his studies,
and one day, he became a mage
in the Imperial Army.
However...
He was still young and arrogant,
and he started chafing
at the limits of magic
and his blood reality.
It wasn't long before
he outright began
to hate the magic he once loved.
But through it all, he
never gave up his dream
of becoming a Mage of Justice.
That was because he
had someone very close
who supported him.
Hold on, is this story about--
Then, on one mission,
that arrogant young
mage failed that girl.
His arrogance became
foolishness and he let her die.
[SISTINE gasps]
[GLENN] Her death made
him more disenchanted
than ever before.
So, he gave up being
a Mage of Justice,
and became an
unemployed shut-in.
And that's the end.
That's sad.
[GLENN sighs]
To be honest,
I don't know why.
In that moment,
it felt like the right move.
Maybe I just wanna help you
solve the sky castle mystery.
And maybe if you make
that dream a reality,
I can finally atone
for losing Sara.
All I know for sure
is when that bastard said
you were wasting
your life studying it,
something inside me snapped.
Before I knew it,
I threw my glove.
No matter what it took,
in that moment,
I just wanted to hurt him.
And that's that.
So in the end,
you just got overly
emotional and lashed out.
[GLENN]
Yes. In a way.
Unbelievable.
You're like a toddler.
[GLENN]
Hey, I'm right here.
[SISTINE sighs]
You know...
I actually feel pretty good.
I mean, what Leos
said does hurt,
but it's the truth.
My grandfather was brilliant.
I'm nowhere near his ability.
The more I study magic,
the more I realize
that and struggle
with losing my love for it.
But now, I have someone.
Someone who supports my dream,
all because they really
want to see me succeed,
and that makes me happy.
So I'm going to work
harder than ever.
Those who accomplish big things
are those who never
give up on their dreams.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[laughing]
Radars for the win!
After all, I wouldn't
be much of a professor
if I didn't support
the dreams of my students!
Hey, don't get too
full of yourself.
Really, now,
"marrying into money."
Couldn't you have
been more tactful?
No, I seriously would
like to do that one day.
Doesn't matter who!
Oh, just shut up!
[LEOS]
I have met many men,
but you are the most
cowardly, Glenn Radars.
You weave a moving
fable of dreams and failure
and then claim
it's your life story.
Anyone can tell
you're only looking
to garner her sympathy.
Leos?
Professor,
since my official work
involves researching
military-grade magic,
I have clearance for accessing
the Imperial Army's
most confidential files.
I know your whole story.
The truth of what
really happened to Sara.
Tell me.
Aren't you "Glenn the Fool"?
All right, buddy.
Shut the hell up and get out
before I make you.
Time catches up.
A man with your past
doesn't have the right
to live a normal life.
How can you be a professor
when your hands
are still dripping wet
with the blood of your old life?
[GLENN]
I said shut up.
I'm not warning you again.
If you say one more thing,
then tomorrow's duel
is gonna start early.
I'll settle this beef
right here and now.
Um, Professor?
There's a place and
a job far better suited
to your talents than "teacher."
Go home to it.
Back to your old spot in
the Imperial Mage Corps
Special Forces.
Number Zero.
"The Fool," Glenn Radars.
[GLENN]
There's three.
Told ya to shut up!
My, my, Radars.
You're so quick to fight.
The Army's
close-combat technique?
What the hell?
--[GLENN yelps]
--[SISTINE] Professor!
[GLENN grunts]
No way, those are tulpas!
Oh, no!
Tulpas are imaginary beings
manifested into our world.
The summoner enters
a trance and wills them
into existence through
the power of suggestion!
That's exactly right.
You've studied well, Sistine.
Impressive.
There is a secret
branch of alchemy.
one that's focused on the
creation of imaginary beings.
That is the tulpas' source!
And they're powerful, indeed.
Especially against you.
What do you think,
Professor Radars?
Instead of summoning
them with a spell,
I used my trance-powered
imagination!
Which means,
since they're not a product
of normal magic, Fool's World
won't work against them!
[GLENN yells]
Professor!
[GLENN grunts]
[LEOS]
What a letdown.
I was expecting you
to be much stronger.
Our duel's still
on for tomorrow.
It'd behoove you to
approach that clash
with more seriousness.
[SISTINE]
Wait!
Glenn's nothing but
a beaten dog now.
[SISTINE]
Stop it, Leos!
I want to talk, honey.
Let... go!
If you don't shut up,
I'll make it so one ever
sees your face again!
[SISTINE]
Leos.
Do you accept my proposal?
You don't have
the right to say no.
By the way, let's talk
about your best friend, Rumia.
You've been protecting her,
haven't you?
Her real name and her power.
How do you know that?
[LEOS]
Let's also talk Re=L Rayford.
I'm sure there are dozens
of underground groups
who'd just love to
prick her with needles
and turn her into a lab rat.
[SISTINE] This isn't
the boy I grew up with.
I shouldn't have to
threaten your friends
for you to say yes.
I mean, you've been in love
with me your whole life, right?
[SISTINE]
Professor, help me!
[SISTINE] The next morning,
Professor Radars
didn't show up for the duel.
In fact, he never returned
to the school again.