Why are you doing this?
Talk to me, Re=L!
[RE=L]
I wish I had another choice.
But if I'm not dedicating
myself to my brother
and this cause,
then what am I living for?
Please help me.
It's you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm too late.
[GLENN gasps]
[groans]
[ALBERT] You're as
resilient as ever, Glenn.
I guess I owe you pretty big.
[ALBERT]
You should thank Miss Fibel.
Without her assistance,
the Reviver spell
never would have worked.
[ALBERT]
Her mana capacity is impressive.
[GLENN chuckles]
I've had my
suspicions for a while.
You really are amazing,
white cat.
A pain in my ass, but,
most the good ones are.
[ALBERT] We may be able to
count on her in our mission
to free the princess.
Let's not be stupid.
She's a kid, Albert.
She stays.
So what are we up against?
[GLENN]
Damn it, Re=L.
[ALBERT] I warned you to be
careful when it came to her.
What else did you see coming?
Did you think the Researchers
of Divine Wise-Assery
might show up here too?
I did.
One of our investigations
revealed a suspicious
flow of money.
Someone sending
a lot of new funding
to the white alchemy lab.
We probed further,
and found a likely connection
between the Researchers
and the lab's director,
Burks Blaumohn.
Then why didn't you tell me
the last time we talked,
when you knew we
were coming here?!
[GLENN]
Oh, of course.
Because you were
using Rumia as bait
to draw them out.
Did that come from
military command?
Or your precious leadership?
Damn you!
You could have helped!
I'm sure you know
why I couldn't object.
'Cause if they turn
their eyes on you,
they could learn
the truth about Re=L.
I get you were in a bind,
but that doesn't excuse
you letting this happen.
Rumia's been through so much
and now you've used her
for convenience!
My superiors are dishonorable
for issuing this order.
Going along with it
makes me just as bad.
I don't deny it.
But I've given Re=L her chance,
and now I'm done with mercy.
If she continues to stand
on the wrong side,
then I will destroy her.
No, that's not the answer.
Re=L's just confused.
We have to show her the truth.
I should have done
that two years ago
back when I found her.
But now she's siding
with her brother, right?
You honestly think she's
going to listen to you?
I'll make her!
She's gonna listen even
if I have to pound it
into her stubborn little head!
You've got some nerve
playing the hero.
You ran away.
Abandoned your comrades
without a single word.
If you want to understand
Re=L's betrayal,
then you should
start with your own.
You broke her heart.
I'm not sure you even
deserve to save her.
You blame me.
Well blame yourself!
Look, I know,
and I'm not gonna argue
with any of that, okay?
I screwed up.
I know don't deserve
to be her friend!
But I am her teacher
and she needs my help!
You haven't changed.
And that why's
despite all else,
I keep choosing to
put my faith in you.
[GLENN grunts]
[GLENN] You ass!
What was that for?
That was for you disappearing.
Now I can forgive you.
Whoa, you kept it?
[ALBERT] My priority is
rescuing the princess.
If the situation requires
me to kill Re=L to do that,
I'll shoot without regret.
And I warn you
not to complain.
[GLENN] You always were
a tough nut to crack.
Mr. Serious-pants over
here says you helped me.
Thanks, Sistine.
Once again.
[KASH] Hey. What's the
professor up to now?
And that soldier who's with him.
[SISTINE]
Professor?
I couldn't stop her
from taking Rumia.
I just froze.
[RUMIA whimpering]
[RUMIA yells]
[BURKS laughing]
Yes! Ha!
Look! It's working!
Project Revive Life
will succeed at last!
With me at the helm!
Though I can't take sole credit.
You gathered all three elements.
And you even
persuaded an enemy
to switch sides and
bring us the Amplifier.
I have to say, you're quite
a resourceful young man.
You honor me with
your praise, Director.
I just knew we had to capture
the Amplifier somehow.
Since we lack the
original spell-caster,
it was the only way.
You should feel privileged
you're contributing
to this important work,
young lady.
[RUMIA whimpering]
[BURKS] I'm surprised you
still have the energy
to look at me.
In that case, enjoy the view!
Like most people,
you probably think
the Researchers of
Divine Wisdom are evil.
But as I see it,
the Imperial Family
are the true purveyors
of terror in this land.
It's enough to make me sick!
[BURKS chuckles]
An empire led
by a family like that
deserves a swift downfall
if you ask me.
That's enough, Burks.
You've had your fun.
What do you know about them?
What have they done
that's so wrong?
[RUMIA yelling]
You'll lose. I know it!
How are you feeling, Re=L?
Everything all right?
How clever.
So that's what he's up to.
[GLENN]
Magic signals?
[ALBERT]
Yes.
After the incident at
the magic competition,
I planted the first
on the princess,
to tell me her
whereabouts at any time.
[GLENN] So that's how
you know where she is?
[ALBERT] No, unfortunately
that one was dispelled.
But I planted another one.
On Eleanor Chalet.
[ELEANOR]
Impressive work, Mr. Frazer.
The Professor!
[BURKS] They will not
impede our progress.
One of my creations
will make sure of that.
[GLENN]
No security, huh?
That's nice of them.
[ALBERT] This will go
quickly if that's the case.
[GLENN]
Hello, nurse!
[LION CHIMERA growling]
[ALBERT]
Roar, flame lion!
[ELEANOR chuckles]
Surely you didn't think
the beast would stop them.
They've been trained by the
Mage Corps, Mr. Blaumohn.
Curse them both!
[SISTINE] What was the
point of all that training
with the Professor if I can't
even help when it counts?
[knocking]
[door opens]
[WENDY]
Sistine, what happened?
Where's Rumia?
This is bad, isn't it?
[GLENN]
So how's your chimera trivia?
[ALBERT] The military
experimented with them
for a while.
But they were so dangerous
the project was shelved.
You think you know a tour
guide and then he tries
to kill you.
Hmph. Well, looks like we're
getting a two-for-one deal.
[TORTOISE CHIMERA growls]
Someone put on
big boy pants today.
[TORTOISE CHIMERA growling]
[BURKS laughing]
Look at them!
Fleeing like roaches
from my jeweled beast!
Professor...
Like I told you, Eleanor.
They're powerless
against my alchemy!
We'll see about that.
[TORTOISE CHIMERA roars]
[GLENN] Now return thyself
to the cycle of providence,
the five elements to elements,
and sever the link
woven between images
and the truth.
I declare that all
creation shall perish here
at the distant ends of the void.
Extinction Ray!
[TORTOISE CHIMERA growls]
What? That can't be!
[ELEANOR chuckles]
You clearly don't
know your enemy.
Professor Radars
continues to impress.
[BURKS]
Professor, please!
He's a substitute, isn't he?
I'm not scared of some
magic teacher temp!
I'll make him breathe his last!
[ELEANOR]
Take note.
I'll leave the rest to you
and your little sister.
Understood, ma'am.
After all, I can't die here.
There's too much work to do.
[KASH]
What do you mean?
You're being totally vague!
[SISTINE]
I'm sorry, that's all I can say.
But the Professor's handling it.
We just need to stay
here until he gets back.
Can we really just wait?
What if Rumia and
Re=L don't come back
while we're twiddling
our thumbs?
[WENDY]
Don't talk like that!
They'll come back!
[CECIL]
You don't know!
Yeah, and waiting
here won't help!
We should look for them too!
No, it's too dangerous!
[KY] So we abandon them
'cause we're scared?
She didn't say that.
She means searching blind
could make things worse!
We know the Professor
can be lazy and annoying
and sometimes even a bastard.
But he's shown us all
that we can trust him
when it counts, right?
But we don't know
what's going on
or what happened to the girls.
What if this time it's something
he can't handle alone?
Or what if he picks now to be
the moron version of himself?
[ALBERT] Re=L and the
princess should be up ahead.
[GLENN]
Look who's come to greet us!
I feel so V.I.P!
[BURKS growls]
Now you die!
[BURKS (MONSTER) roars]
[GLENN]
He's even changed his own body.
Alchemy addicts are sad.
I'll stay here and
handle this monstrosity.
You go on.
Aw, thanks.
Just try not to have
too much fun.
[ALBERT]
Lightning Spear.
[BURKS (MONSTER) growls]
I suggest you focus on me.
[KASH]
Enough talk!
I'm ready for action!
[GIBUL] Tsk!
Oh spare us the theatrics, Kash.
If the bastard didn't
want our help,
we shouldn't be trying
to give it to him.
You're just too cool
for anything, aren't you.
Don't you care
about our friends?
[SISTINE]
That's not it, Kash!
He means the Professor
had a reason.
For not wanting us to come.
Right, Gibul?
I'm worried about
Re=L and the professor,
and Rumia is like
a sister to me.
So yeah.
Waiting here feels like torture.
But if we go, what are
we going to accomplish?
We know magic!
We could help with
whatever's out there!
Doubtful.
We'd turn into more
people he has to save.
[SISTINE]
I know it's hard, for everyone,
but the professor
asked us to stay.
So I'm begging you to trust him.
Yeah, okay, we get it already.
Sorry. I guess
I'm just a worrier.
It's probably less of
a crisis than I think.
Even if it is serious,
the professor can handle it.
Remember how he took
out those terrorists
all by himself?
I believe in him.
Thanks, guys, really.
[WENDY]
Why are you crying, Sistine?
Is there something else?
[SISTINE]
No.
It's just the stress.
[RAINER]
It's almost complete.
But I fear those two vicious
mages will be here soon.
You'll defeat them.
Won't you, my dear sister?
And keep me safe?
Of course.
You're my only
reason for living.
Good girl.
Professor!
Hey, Rumia! What's hanging?
And that's a pun I
immediately regret.
Thank goodness you're safe.
I've been worried sick, sir.
Strung up like a slab of meat
and she's worried about me?
[GLENN]
Re=L!
Enough with the mute routine!
Aren't you gonna say something
after literally backstabbing me?
And you, Lord Derpy Face.
Did you have to dangle my
hottie student in chains?
'Cause I'm not saying
I have a bondage fetish,
but if I did that
would be distracting!
'Kay?
Our director does have
a flair for the dramatic.
He like dramatic
beat-downs too?
Stop there.
Don't come any
closer to my brother.
Thanks, Re=L.
I knew I could count on my sis.
Make sure he doesn't
interfere with our work.
I understand.
I beseech creation.
Grant unto my hands
a great blade.
[GLENN]
Come on, Re=L.
You sure you want to fight me?
I'd say you've taken this
little prank far enough.
Talk all you want, Glenn.
I'll protect my brother
to the very end.
[GLENN]
You idiot!
This is all just a trick!
Your brother's as dead as
this chode's about to be!
Shut up!
Yelling at me won't
make it less true!
How can you deny it when
he's standing right there?!
Listen, Re=L, you're confused!
[RE=L]
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
[GLENN] Damn it, she doesn't
want to listen to me.
How do I make her see?
[GLENN]
Come on, Re=L.
Bring it on!
[RE=L yells]
[GLENN]
Albert's right.
It's my fault for not
telling her the truth,
and for running
away without her.
But I'm not running now.
She just has to hear me!
[RE=L yelling]
Hey! Stop!
Don't do this, Re=L,
I know he's trying to help you!
Don't hurt him!
He's too important!
To all of us!
And you're important
to us too, Re=L.
We care about you.
Don't you remember the stars?
[RE=L gasps]
[GLENN]
Now's my chance!
[GLENN] Turning on Rumia
must've been hard.
So you really love
your brother that much?
Yes, he means everything to me.
That's why I've decided
to dedicate my life to him.
I guess I didn't want to
believe 'cause I was jealous
he meant so much to you.
[RE=L]
What are you saying?
I'm saying if you'd
do this for him,
he must be a great guy and
I should give him a chance.
So, introduce us.
What's his name?
Why are you asking me that now?
Re=L!
He's stalling. Finish him!
Oh, come on,
it's a simple question.
Tell me his name
and I'll back down.
Don't listen,
he's playing mind games!
[GLENN]
Say it, Re=L. I'm waiting.
His name?
[GLENN]
What's wrong?
[RE=L] My brother's name.
My brother's--
[gasps]
My head hurts.
What's happening?
My brother's name--
What's wrong with me?
Why can't I remember it?
It doesn't matter if you forgot!
I'm still your brother!
[RE=L]
Huh?
[GLENN] Let the plate
of order tip to starboard.
[GLENN]
It was a risky bet.
Get off me.
You can't win.
This isn't my strength
you're feeling.
It's gravity.
Gravity manipulation?
Just sit tight,
and I'll take care of this.
You get away from my sister!
[GLENN]
Shut up.
Your con-game's over!
[GLENN growls]
How could you?!
I knew when you said Re=L.
Next time you want
to pose as her brother,
you should go with
the girl's actual name!
We called it
"Project Revive Life."
Or for short, Project Re=L.
[RE=L]
That's right.
My brother's name was Sion.
[RAINER] I decided to
name Illushia's copy
after the project.
Has a nice ring,
don't you think?
[RE=L (ILLUSHIA)]
Re=L?
[SION]
Rainer. We need to stop this.
How many innocent people
have we sacrificed
just to make this one clone?
You can leave the group with us.
I've already made arrangements.
The Imperial Court Mage C--
[gasps]
[SION coughs]
--[SION] Rainer...
--[RE=L (ILLUSHIA)] No!
[SION]
Illushia, run!
I don't need you
anymore either, Illushia.
Since I already have your
three elements in hand,
I'll put you to rest
right next to your brother.
[RE=L] I remember now
who I--no, what I am.
[RAINER] Two years ago,
Sion betrayed the project
and reported us to the
Imperial Court Mage Corps,
which led to them
raiding our lab
and setting us back till now.
[GLENN]
Yeah, I know all about it.
I'm the one Sion contacted.
[SION]
The project's almost finished.
All they need now
is my original spell
to complete the ritual.
I'm the only one
there who can cast it.
If I leave, they're stuck.
But Glenn. If I help you...
There are two others
I want to save.
We've been through
everything together.
Friends our whole lives.
And their names?
Illushia and Rainer, sir.
[GLENN] He went to
arrange your extraction,
then we lost contact
so we raided the lab.
But Sion was already dead.
And his sister was
too wounded to save.
[GLENN] All I could do
was protect the copy.
The manufactured girl
who had inherited
Illushia's Astral Code,
and all her memories
right up to the moment
of her death.
The copy.
That's me.
I thought I had altered your
memories to suit my needs,
but I guess I didn't
have time for a full scrub
before we were raided.
Oh, well, the first
draft's always junk.
Look, you bastard.
Don't talk about her like that.
But it's just the truth,
she is junk!
A broken egg.
Damn you!
Thunder emperor,
pierce with your
brilliant lance of light!
Let me introduce the
new and improved model.
Aw, hell.
Now these girls
are real perfection.
I eliminated all
those pesky emotions,
which makes them so
much easier to control.
I call them my little
army of puppets.
Now, girls!
Destroy these intruders!
[GLENN grunts]
[GLENN]
Woo!
That was way too close.
Why protect something worthless?
I'm just a copy.
I'm not real!
[GLENN]
Shut up, dummy.
You answered your own question.
I wouldn't risk my life
if you were worthless!
But I'm a doll.
What worth can I have?
Nah.
A doll wouldn't
be moping like that!
[grunting]
I don't see you
as a doll or copy.
And neither does
white cat, or Rumia,
or the rest of the class!
That's right, you're our friend!
There, you see?
But I've been cruel.
I've done terrible
things to you.
And Sistine and everyone else!
[GLENN grunts]
Then apologize later!
--[GLENN yells]
--[RUMIA] Professor!
[GLENN]
That freaking hurts!
[GLENN] The trick is to find
something you can care about
and just live for that.
Forget about the nature of life.
All that hippie crap's
just gonna strain
what little brains
you have left.
[RE=L]
Something I can care about?
I'm sorry, my sisters.
I know it's a selfish choice,
but I'll live a life
for all of us.
[RE=L yelling]
No, this can't be!
Thunder emperor,
pierce with your
brilliant lance of light!
Magic hour's over.
Now it's time for The Fool.
Sorry for this, Rumia.
Just close your eyes.
It'll be done soon.
[RUMIA]
That look...
It's like when I first met him.
[RAINER]
Please, no...
Don't kill me.
[GLENN]
Say goodnight, mullet.
[gun clicks]
[GLENN] Did you really think
I'd blow your brains out
in front of two of
my own students?
Just stay away from my kids.
Or I will end you!
[BURKS (MONSTER) roaring]
[ALBERT]
Death to you.
Even last rites
shall be foregone.
Repent for eternity as you burn
in limbo's crimson flames.
[BURKS (MONSTER)]
I can't die!
Heaven chose me!
[GROUP chattering]
[SISTINE]
Rumia!
Re=L!
[crying]
[GIBUL] In theory,
you receive the ball
based on its angle
to the ground.
[yells]
[GROUP chattering]
It really is a precious
sight, isn't it.
Hell yeah.
Look at all those swimsuits!
And volleyball has a
very high bounce factor!
You know that's not
what I was talking about.
This moment.
Their happiness.
That's what you fought
so hard to protect.
Right, Glenn?
Who can say.
[ELEANOR]
Yes. I have it.
The entire Project Revive
Life ritual is now ours.