[STUDENTS cheering]
It really is a precious
sight, isn't it.
Hell yeah.
Look at all those swimsuits!
And volleyball has a
very high bounce factor!
You know that's not
what I was talking about.
This moment. Their happiness.
That's what you fought
so hard to protect.
Right, Glenn?
Who can say.
[GROUP chattering]
You mind?
[laughs]
Nope! Here it comes!
Thank you, Professor!
She looks like her.
Who?
Sara Silvers, of course.
[GRANDMASTER]
Judging from her usefulness
with Project Revive Life,
do you believe the powers
of Princess Ermiana
are nearing full maturity?
Yes.
So, how would you like us
to proceed, Grandmaster?
[GRANDMASTER]
Let us be patient, and observe.
[ELEANOR]
Understood, my liege.
But there are those
within the organization
who are plotting to bring
about the Princess's
rebirth themselves.
Should I intervene?
[GRANDMASTER]
Deal with them as you see fit.
[ELEANOR]
Yes, Grandmaster.
[GRANDMASTER] After all,
the choices each of you make
will be the blocks
that build my story.
[MR. FIBEL]
We're so glad you're here!
[MRS. FIBEL] Please. Eat as
much as you like, sweetie.
That's right, do you
like roast beef?
Because if not we'd be happy
to serve something else.
I know you wanna
be a good host,
but Re=L is just shy by nature.
So, maybe dial it down?
[MR. FIBEL]
Oh, so you mean it's not because
she hates the food?
[SISTINE]
Of course not.
Oh, what a relief!
I was literally shaking
from worry!
You silly-willy!
[SISTINE, RUMIA chuckle]
All right, Re=L.
I just have to ask you this.
Sistine and Rumia
are always going on
about that new Professor Radars.
What do you think about him?
Do you like him, too?
For me, everything
starts with Glenn.
That's some endorsement!
He really must be a
remarkable young man!
Uh, I'm not sure
she meant it that way.
[RUMIA chuckles]
Please. Just try the soup.
And the fresh salad!
Come on, Dad.
It's too much.
She can't eat it all!
[MRS. FIBEL] Oh, dear, we'll be
heading to the capital tomorrow.
Can you run the house
while we're gone?
Sure. I always do.
Say, that reminds me.
I wanted to tell
Sistine something.
I feel like it's important, but
I can't remember what it was.
Beats me!
I'm not sure what
to say, Sistine.
[SISTINE]
Hm?
About what happened.
Don't worry. It's over.
But I haven't apologized.
[SISTINE]
You don't have to. Okay?
Even so. I'm sorry.
And... and thank you.
You're both so precious to me.
You know that, right?
[SISTINE gasps]
I-I'm sorry...
Professor Arfonia.
Melgalius's Sky Castle, huh?
Your grandfather spent
years researching this too,
--didn't he?
--Yes.
I'm hoping to carry his torch
and unlock the mystery.
Though it's stumped
so many others
I'm not sure I can.
The ones who
accomplish true greatness
are the foolish who
keep pressing onward.
The ones who accomplish nothing
are the wise who
know when to quit.
Is that a quote from someone?
[CELICA]
It's from me.
Give it all you've got.
The ones who
accomplish true greatness
are the foolish who keep
pressing onward, right?
The underground labyrinth.
If I believe my own words,
I need to go in again.
Yo.
[SISTINE gasps]
[GLENN]
Hey!
[SISTINE] The library doesn't
really suit you, Professor.
What are you talking about?
I'm basically a walking
tome of knowledge.
That's too stupid
to even comment on.
Well, you're no fun.
By the way...
Yeah, what?
The other day,
when I nearly croaked...
I heard you not only
helped cast Reviver,
you kept me breathing
until it was ready, too.
[SISTINE gasps]
I'd hate to be an
ungrateful jerk-wad.
So thanks, kid.
Uh... Why does your face
look like it's glowing?
Sisti. Is something wrong?
Did you make her cry?
I've committed my life
to protecting my friends.
Whoa, down, girl!
[RE=L]
I beseech creation.
Grant unto my hands
a great blade.
[GLENN]
Aw, son of a bitch!
[yells]
Come on, stop!
I'm an innocent man!
[yells]
[GLENN screams]
Look out!
Splendid flow of wind, pay heed.
[GLENN yells]
[LEOS]
Ha!
What are the chances
I'd run into you
the moment I arrived?
Good morning, Sistine.
Shut the front door...!
Sensin' weird vibes here.
[LEOS]
My name is Leos.
Leos Kleitos.
I've been invited
to this fine academy
as a guest instructor,
and I'm also Sistine's fiancé.
[GLENN, RE=L, RUMIA]
What?!
Yes, that's it!
[MRS. FIBEL]
Huh?
I was supposed to tell
Sistine that Leos was coming
to the academy today.
Oh! I forgot too.
Now wait just a minute, Leos!
Since when are we engaged?
[laughs]
We made a promise to each
other when we were children.
Don't you remember that?
[SISTINE] But that was pretend!
Like make believe!
Dude, you're not
really serious, right?
I mean, you can't be!
If you want to
pair off with her,
I'll give you a shovel,
'cause you'll be digging
your own grave.
You shut your cake hole.
I'll ask you kindly to refrain
from insulting
my future wife, sir.
I will defend her.
Hold on, Leos.
He's just joking, okay?
The professor's
just really, dumb.
The Professor?
Does that mean--?
Are you... Glenn Radars?
What, am I on a
"Most Wanted" list now?
There's been a lot
of talk about you
at the Kleitos Magic Academy.
That's the school where I teach,
if you haven't guessed.
A promising new
instructor making waves
at Alzano Imperial.
People can't help but gossip.
They say unlike
the current trend,
to cram in as many
spells as we can by rote,
you are more focused on
a deeper comprehension
of the fundamentals,
and their practical application.
There's even talk
of original spells.
That would be rare.
I would love to sit in on
one of your lectures sometime.
I don't know.
There might be a waiting list.
[RICK]
Leos Kleitos.
He's a candidate to be the
next head of the countdom.
[HALLEY] Sure, from the
Imperial United Society!
He's famous!
I told his school
about our professor's
medical leave of
absence on a lark.
I didn't expect them to send
one of the greatest professors
they have to help us!
I'm so excited!
We're so lucky!
But you're right to be
surprised, Headmaster.
Don't you think them
sending him here is bizarre?
Suppose so.
Don't give me that.
You're just worried
this actual talent
is going to overshadow
that loser apprentice.
I wish that was the case.
It would make this
a lot more simple.
Maybe it was only
a child's game to you,
but not to me.
I love you profoundly, Sistine.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Wow, congratulations, white cat!
I had you pegged as a
life-long spinster myself!
I guess you can be loved!
Man! Just goes to show
there's a weirdo
for every type of fetish!
Oh, you've got
some planning to do.
Well I'll be happy to
give a toast at your wedding,
as long as you have an open bar.
--Shut up, you idiot!
--[GLENN yelling]
Nice distance.
Sistine's so mad.
Why is that?
[RUMIA chuckles]
I think this is turning
into a pretty big deal.
[LEOS] And that is the
simplest way to explain
Zaiser's formula
for magic energy
transduction performance.
Up until recently,
most attack spells
employed by the
Imperial military
were one of three types.
Heat, cold, or shock.
I hope now, with this
elegant formula in mind,
you can understand why.
Take Shock Bolt, for example.
It's perhaps our
most basic spell.
Yet if you can
apply these lessons,
you can increase its
output significantly.
Since wind spells
don't function this way,
they have less military use.
Yet they do have other merits,
which I will be discussing
in our next lecture.
--[bell ringing]
--And that's the bell.
Thanks for listening.
I hope I've helped.
[STUDENTS clapping]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[GLENN] That was
pitch-freaking-perfect.
He made the Material
Force Theory
totally accessible
to these kids,
and that's a concept half
the common mage troops
in the military don't
fully understand.
But even if they can learn now,
that doesn't mean they should.
If they're smart and follow
the theory to its end,
they'll realize even
Shock Bolt can kill
if you boost it enough.
They're learning to
harness huge power
without learning the
judgment to back it up.
They don't know
what power means.
What it can do to you--
what consequences feel like.
They just know it exists.
I'm guessing you
don't really approve
of this lesson, do you,
Professor Radars?
[GLENN]
You guessed right.
You tell us not to be dumb,
and to always think hard
before we summon
any new power.
To learn to use magic
and not let it use us.
I think I finally
understand your point.
Well you don't have to worry.
I don't think any
student you've taught
will make that mistake.
You've made sure of that.
Whatever.
I'm probably just jealous
Mr. Monocoled Dreamboat
is more competent
than I expected.
Hey, great job, white cat.
You must have quick
claws for that catch!
You're not funny.
[LEOS]
Sistine.
How was that?
I want to hear
your candid opinion.
Uh... Okay.
I thought it was phenomenal!
Well that's a relief to hear.
Especially from you.
You've established quite a
reputation with other teachers.
Just a few.
As I see it,
I've cleared my first hurdle
in proving myself
a suitable husband.
I'm so glad.
Can you please stop saying that?
At least in public?
[KASH, CECIL]
Yeah!
Sistine.
Would you join me
for a walk outside?
There's more I'd
like to talk about.
I don't know.
Does it have to be now?
I have plans.
Of course it can wait.
It's up to you.
Though it is something I think
we should discuss eventually.
I'm sorry, Rumia.
Is it okay if I go?
Shall we?
[RUMIA]
Professor...
Yeah, what's up?
Can I...
Can I ask you a favor?
Doesn't this remind
you of our childhood?
Walking side by side
on beautiful grounds?
Yes, it does.
[LEOS] The passage of
time is cruel, isn't it?
I was so convinced what
we had would never change
that I've taken our
relationship for granted.
[SISTINE]
Yeah, I guess I have, too.
The years sneak up on you.
It takes work to keep
a friendship close.
If we don't make
a conscious effort,
then soon we'll just be
fond memories to each other
without that real connection.
I still don't get why
you want me to help
peep on someone else's romance.
It's just a hunch.
This has creeper
written all over it.
[LEOS] Well I for one want to
make sure that doesn't happen,
and I think I know the way.
May we stop?
Sistine Fibel.
Will you marry me?
Whoa!
He just popped the
question out of nowhere!
Holy crap!
Rumia, I take it back,
this is a great show!
[RUMIA groans]
You're worried.
What's wrong?
I can't put my finger on it.
I just have a bad feeling.
Oh, I get it.
Like women's intuition, right?
We'll talk about that later.
But first let's
enjoy the drama!
Um, Leos...
I care about you,
but I'm afraid my answer
has to be no.
What?
Uh...
And why not?
I promised my grandfather
to solve the mystery
of Melgalius's Sky Castle.
To do that, I've got a lot
more to learn about magic,
and I can't afford
to be pulled two ways.
I'm sorry.
[laughs]
You haven't changed at all.
I can't believe
you're still focusing
on that ridiculous fantasy.
[SISTINE gasps]
Magic archeology.
The exploration of
ancient ruins and artifacts,
with the ultimate goal
of unraveling the mysteries
of past civilizations
and recreating spells
forgotten by time.
It's an alluring idea,
but no one has
ever accomplished it,
and the Sky Castle is
the most opaque of all.
Devoting your talents
to the same fool's errand
would be a meaningless,
tragic squandering.
A fool's errand?
Your grandfather was brilliant.
If he hadn't been
obsessed with that castle
imagine how much more
he could have contributed
to a useful field.
Please, Sistine.
Listen to reason
and join me in my work.
With your assistance
we could revolutionize
military magic.
I'm sorry, Leos.
You're a great mage and
you have wonderful dreams.
But so do I and
I won't give them up.
I want you to have dreams.
I simply don't want you
to waste your life.
Stop trying to tear
her down, you shitbag!
Professor?
[GLENN] Walk the path
you believe in, white cat!
And never forget,
in your own life story,
you're the main character,
not this douche!
[chuckles] Nailed it.
You're sticking
your nose in again?
And spying on us, too?
I beg your pardon, colleague,
this is not your business.
So stay out.
[GLENN]
Oh...
You're wrong.
It is his business.
Uh... I'm sorry, what?
Explain, Sistine.
What are you telling me?
[SISTINE]
Well, uh...
I'm saying...
I'm saying the
professor and I, uh...
We're madly in love, okay?
And secretly engaged!
[gasping]
[SISTINE] That's why
I can't marry you, Leos.
[GLENN chuckles]
Well, I guess the
white cat's out of the bag!
[laughing]
[LEOS]
Lies!
My Sistine would never
fall for a buffoon like you!
You're wrong, pal!
She fell and fell hard.
In fact she just fell into my
bed last night--it was hot.
Shut up, you moron!
Stop exaggerating!
All we've done is kiss, okay?
Kiss?! You kissed that cretin?
I'm lying, though,
not technically,
if you count mouth to mouth.
Face it, goocher.
White cat's gonna marry me.
So give it up.
I will not.
Anyone who truly
cares about Sistine
would try to help her
see the truth
before it's too late.
You're not fit
to be with this lady.
And yet somehow I'm the one
she's actually picked.
Them's the breaks, cyclops.
Steel yourself, Glenn Radars.
You're going to regret
making an enemy out of me.
Let's all calm down.
Wow.
You're showing your true colors.
You'd be bad news for her.
I guess we have
to make this official.
What's that mean?
[GLENN] We'll settle this
the old-fashioned way.
Let's duel!
You got the balls to accept?
Nothing would please me more.
We can agree on
the details later.
I've got a class to teach.
Excuse me.
Well, that was fun!
Can you be serious for once?
Hey, come to think of it...
This is actually a sweet plan!
If I'm your husband,
I won't have to work at all!
I can be a kept man!
[SISTINE]
Idiot!
So, that's the gist!
I'll get hitched to white cat,
live off her money and
spend the rest of my days
as a shut-in who
never wears pants!
We just need to win!
So I'm training you all
for mage squad combat!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Uh, Sistine, is he joking?
If it's your duel,
why do we have to fight?
Yeah, we didn't
challenge the guy!
Well, the terms are his call.
Which sucks, I know.
Damned tricky weasel
wants it to be a battle
of our teaching skills.
Sorry to be blunt,
but doesn't that
mean you're screwed?
He's like a teaching prodigy.
Just means we'll
have to cram harder!
[STUDENTS]
What?!
Hey, I'll make it
worth it, I promise.
Once I'm stinking rich,
I won't forget you guys.
[ALBERT] Sounds like you're
right back in the deep end.
Competing for a woman
you don't even love.
You're despicable.
Have you even stopped
to think what she wants?
I'm more worried for me.
Can you imagine me
working the rest of my life?
Enough about that.
Why'd you call me here, anyway?
[ALBERT] I've received word
that "Angel's Dust"
has been smuggled
into this city.
No way!
I thought the means
to create that junk
had been destroyed during
that whole thing last year.
Yes, we thought so as well.
That drug turns
people into husks,
mindless puppets, to control.
That case disgusted me.
Answer's no.
I haven't even asked you yet.
You don't have to.
I knew how you'd react.
So, I came to tell you
not to get involved.
[ALBERT] Honestly, hearing
that it's being used again
makes me wonder if
Sara died for nothing.
I'm not gonna let that
happen again, Albert.
Not this time.
This time?
Wow.
[chuckles]
I was right.
You do see Sara in that girl.
[GLENN]
Shut up.
[SARA]
Don't be embarrassed, Glenn.
I like it.
I think it's a beautiful dream.
[SARA] A mage of justice,
always coming to the rescue.
I often wish there were
someone like that in the world.
You should take
pride in that dream,
and cling to it.
That's what I think.
[GLENN] All right, white dog,
don't make it a thing.
[SARA laughs]
Given the job we do,
who wouldn't welcome
a hero in their corner?
You're fine, Sara,
don't worry about a thing.
I'll always protect--
[GLENN] W-Wait.
Is that not what you...?
[SARA] Finish!
What were you about to say?
[GLENN] Nothing,
I said nothing, forget it!
[JATICE]
How did it play out, Leos?
Exactly the way you predicted.
[JATICE chuckles]
I mean, really.
It was most uncanny.
Right after I proposed,
Glenn challenged me to a duel.
I'm starting to think
you're some kind of prophet.
[JATICE]
I just know people.
Leos.
Dance your best
against Glenn for me.
You will be laying down
the foundation of my justice.