[bell ringing]
[KASH]
Nah.
You mixed it up;
it's the other way around.
[GLENN]
Okay.
Class today is pretty much
just reading this again.
So you guys can
take it from here.
[SISTINE]
What is wrong with this guy?
Is he doing this every class?
Nothing's changed!
I can't believe he's just
blatantly ignoring an agreement
between mages!
[LYNN]
Excuse me. Sir?
Yeah, what is it?
I still don't understand
how to translate
these runic spells.
[SISTINE]
Don't waste your time.
But Sisti--
There's no point in
asking him anything.
He won't help you.
Even if he could
answer the question,
he won't make the effort.
He doesn't care about magic
or respect it.
[LYNN]
Yeah, but...
[SISTINE]
It's all right.
I'll teach you.
We'll take care of ourselves!
[GLENN]
Why should I care about magic?
Why's it so great?
Figures you'd respond
with ignorance.
Magic is the study of
the world's principles.
What could matter more?
Huh?
The origin and structure
of reality itself.
The natural laws that
govern the entire world.
Magic reveals all that,
helping us understand
forces seen and unseen
and answering the
eternal questions of why
we and this world exist
and what our role can be.
It's humanity's lantern
in the dark,
showing the path to a
greater plane of existence.
That's why magic is great.
Because it empowers us
with understanding.
[GLENN]
But what's its real use?
We can talk all day about
"why this" and "why that"
but what does that
actually accomplish for us?
[SISTINE]
What?
What kind of question is that?
Like I said, it reveals a
higher plane of existence--
[GLENN] And what exactly
is on that higher plane?
What, like gods?
Well, it's just...
[GLENN] I'm asking you
what tangible benefit
humanity gets from magic.
Look at the field of medicine.
It saves people
when they're sick.
Real, practical use
on a massive scale.
That's true for agriculture,
and architecture.
But what about magic?
Is it just me, or does magic
not do crap for people?
That's unfair.
Magic may not feed or house us.
But it provides something
greater than our basic needs.
It's about searching for
the truth behind this world
--and life itself!
--[GLENN] Sorry, my bad.
I've been lying.
The truth is magic's incredibly
useful for one thing.
For killing people!
[SISTINE gasps]
[STUDENTS gasp]
[GLENN]
Think about it.
In the same time it takes to
kill one person with a sword,
the right spell could
kill ten or more!
When it comes to mass murder,
magic is in a class of its own!
[SISTINE]
That's not funny!
[GLENN]
I agree.
Now in the past,
magic and death
have gone hand in hand.
No!
[GLENN] The field of magic
doesn't give us anything good.
It's built on bloodshed.
[SISTINE]
That's not what magic is about!
[GLENN]
What are you kids thinking?
Open your eyes!
You come here every day
to study an art
that's only useful for
causing death and suffering!
Instead of devoting your
life to something so wretched,
why don't you
do something good--
[slap]
[STUDENTS gasp]
Why you...!
I hate you!
[RUMIA]
Sisti!
[door closes]
[GLENN]
Magic is great?
What kind of crap is that?
Little brat.
No...
I think the brat
award goes to me.
Okay, I'm done with this job.
I better practice
groveling when I get home.
If I kowtow hard enough,
Celica just might forgive me.
[GLENN]
Hey, what's going on in there?
A magic circle? Huh.
[RUMIA]
That's weird.
[gasps]
Personal use of this lab's
against the rules, you know.
Oh, hi, Professor.
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to
get some more practice
creating a magic circle.
I'll clean up now.
[GLENN]
It's fine.
Might as well finish.
Thank you, but I
can't get it to work.
[GLENN]
Sure you can, dummy.
Just need more mercury.
You kids are too much.
You're all so hung up
on the forces you can't see
that you don't pay
enough attention
to the stuff in plain sight,
right in front of you.
[GLENN] That shows you
think magic's more sacred
than it really is.
Now, try activating it again.
Use all five phrases,
like in the textbook.
No shortcuts.
[RUMIA]
Okay.
Cycle. Cycle.
Oh, origin of life.
Manifest your path within.
Truth encircled.
You're amazing, Professor.
I've never seen
one so beautiful!
Oh, don't be silly.
It's a glorified parlor trick.
And most of the magic
was your doing, anyway.
[CELICA]
See? Incredible, right?
[RUMIA] Professor Radars,
I think the truth is
you love magic.
[GLENN]
What makes you say that?
It looked like you were
really having fun back there.
You're confused, little lady.
I hate magic with a passion.
[RUMIA laughs]
Is that right?
May I ask what you were
doing before you became
a substitute teacher?
I'm proud to say I was
a freeloading shut-in!
What? A shut-in, sir?
Are you serious?
[GLENN]
You know Celica?
That high and mighty
professor at the academy?
I've been sponging off
her for the past year.
For a year?
What about before that?
[GLENN]
Okay, enough questions.
What, are you launching
an investigation?
It's my turn now.
Why is everyone in
your class so high-strung
when it comes to learning magic?
You take spell-casting
way too seriously.
I don't know.
Guess I can only
speak for myself.
I understand your point
about magic causing damage.
And I want to change that.
And make it truly
helpful to people.
I owe someone a debt
I'd like to repay.
[GLENN]
What do you mean?
[RUMIA]
Three years ago,
when I was banished
from my home...
Right around the time
I started living with Sisti
and her family.
I was captured by a group of
evil mages, and nearly killed.
That's when he came.
A true mage of justice.
He swooped in and saved my life.
[VILLAINS yelling]
[RUMIA]
I sat there, stunned,
as he defeated one
bad mage after another.
It was terrifying.
But that day,
when I saw magic used
for evil and good,
I realized I wanted to
help lead the human race
down the right path.
To use magic as we should.
But to do that,
I need to understand
magic better myself.
I hope if I stay on that road,
it will lead me back to him.
So one day,
I can thank him for saving me
and prove I was worth it.
To repay the man
who gave me light
when I was alone,
crying in the darkness.
That's my reason.
Hold on...
Yes, what is it?
Nah, just forget it.
[RUMIA]
Can I ask you one more thing
before you go, Professor?
Would you mind
apologizing to Sisti?
Magic means a lot to her,
for lots of reasons.
Most of all, I think it
makes her feel connected
to her grandfather,
who passed away.
[GRANDFATHER FIBEL]
One step.
That's all I wished for.
Just one step into
Melgalius's Sky Castle
before I breathed
my last breath.
That was the sole
reason I became a mage.
But it never came to pass.
[SISTINE]
I'll do it!
I promise!
I won't stop until I've become
an even greater mage than you.
And I'll unravel the
mysteries of the sky castle!
[STUDENTS whispering]
[GLENN]
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Look, you know how
much I hate magic.
I've made that perfectly clear,
and I'm not gonna
pretend otherwise for you
or anybody else.
But I went too far.
So I'm sorry.
Anyway, on with stupid class.
[GLENN] Actually, first,
I need to say one more thing.
Every one of you guys....
...is an idiot.
[STUDENTS gasp]
I realized that from the way
you approach these classes.
None of you
understands a single thing
about how magic really works.
[GIBUL] This coming from
a disaster of a mage
who can't even one-line
a chant as simple
as Shock Bolt.
Okay, you've got my ears burning
with that comment, buddy.
It's true; I don't really get
into mana manipulation
and chant reduction stuff.
But come on.
You really think
Shock Bolt is simple?
See? I told you you were stupid.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[GLENN]
But that's okay.
Today, I'm gonna teach you
the truth about Shock Bolt.
We all know the standard chant.
"Thunder sprites, pay heed,
and strike with
your electric shock."
The real shock is he
needs the whole chant.
This was like the
first spell we mastered!
Why's he wasting our time?
And as we all know,
mages with a real talent
for mana manipulation
can shorten it to
"Thunder sprites, shock"
for a quicker attack.
Here's my question for you.
"Thunder sprites, pay heed,
and strike with
your electric shock."
What happens if you split
this three-line chant
into four?
[GIBUL] If you don't pause
in the right places,
the chant will fail.
And the spell won't
function properly.
You want a prize for
being obvious, dumbass?
Of course the spell
won't work as intended.
I'm asking what'll
happen instead.
You'll get a random misfire.
Everyone knows that!
Random, really?
I thought you said
you mastered this spell.
Anyone else want to try?
No?
Fine, then I'll tell you.
The bolt will
curve to the right.
Thunder sprites.
Pay heed.
And strike with your....
...electric shock.
--[GIBUL] No way!
--[WENDY] That's impossible!
That's just one choice.
Make it five lines, like this...
And you shorten the range.
Or drop this part
and the output plummets.
If you're claiming
you've mastered this spell,
you should know all this, right?
Look. In short, magic is
just an advanced form
of autosuggestion.
Self-hypnosis.
We use the runic
language for spells
'cause it's the
most efficient way
to achieve that reshaping
of the human subconscious.
Then it's our minds,
not the spells,
that manipulate the principles
governing reality.
You may think magic's
all about studying
the laws of the world
outside of us.
But you're wrong.
More than anything,
magic is about probing
the heart of mankind.
You're skeptical.
You think spells are
more than just words,
'cause words can't have
so much power, right?
Let's try something.
Hey. White cat.
Excuse me?
Is that supposed to be funny?
I have a proper name,
it's Sistine Fibel--
I love you.
And I've been in love with you
since the first moment we met.
[SISTINE gasps]
[GLENN]
There, you see?
Miss white cat's face
has just turned beet red!
With just a few words,
I affected her mind and
got a physical reaction.
Language influences the
mind to influence the world.
That's all magic--Ah!
You idiot!
Don't throw textbooks!
You're the idiot, idiot!
Idiot! Idiot!
Anyway, let's move on.
Since it is about the language,
the grammar and syntax matter.
By making subtle changes,
you can reshape your
subconscious any way you want.
Okay, how do I explain
the next part?
Here. Just watch.
Paralyze.
Wow.
That was weaker than I expected.
Well...
You get the gist.
You can substitute words too.
That's crazy!
He didn't use one word
from the original spell!
Keywords to activate powers
that have been embedded
deep in your own subconscious.
That's all spells are.
It's an association game.
A minute ago, I gave your
classmate a nickname.
Now what do you think
when you look at her?
--[WENDY] A cat.
--[TERESA] Yeah, a cat.
[GLENN]
Chants work the same way.
Make an association,
and your mind can recall
the power however you want.
It's easy.
So sure, you can translate
and memorize chants
exactly how this
lame textbook says.
But if you don't
understand why it works,
then you'll just be
continuing the same
"magic for dummies" classes
you've apparently been taking
since you came to this school.
[laughs] No thanks.
[GLENN] Right now, you kids are
nothing but mindless mimics
who can recite the
spells you've been told.
But if you want to
become true mages,
you've got some
serious gaps to fill.
Now. We're going back to basics
so you can learn 'em right.
If you're not into that,
you can just sleep.
[CELICA laughs]
I knew he could do it all along!
Just had to put his
mind to it, that's all!
[RICK] His lectures
are becoming so popular,
even students from other classes
have been sneaking in to watch!
Well that's because he
was my greatest apprentice,
who I taught from scratch!
He went here!
[HALLEY]
Damn you, Glenn Radars!
I'll get you out
of this academy.
You'll see!
The first thing you need
to learn about original magic.
It's not any more
special or sacred
than the standard stuff
in your books.
You seem to have this idea
that inventing unique spells
is this huge thing,
like you're not worthy to try.
But trust me,
trying's not a big deal.
The real challenge is
making something better
than existing spells,
which were
painstakingly developed
by countless mages
over the years.
'Cause if it's not better,
what's the point, right?
[GLENN]
Who woulda' thought?
This really isn't so bad.
[CELICA]
Aw, look at you.
Getting all pensive
in the twilight.
I'm glad you're
enjoying your youth.
What do you want now?
Oh, nothing at all.
I just came to say well done.
You've perked up a bit.
Up until recently,
you looked like a caught fish
who'd been dead
for a month or two.
But I've noticed a change.
Now it looks like you've
only been dead for a day.
[GLENN]
Hey!
I know you were worried.
I'm sorry for that.
All righty.
Tomorrow, I leave for
a magic conference.
Normally, you could come, too,
but after Professor Huey's
departure, your class is behind.
You'll have to stay here.
Don't play any weird
pranks on the girls
just because the rest
of the professors are away.
Oh, please!
As if I could be interested
in typical schoolgirls
after living with
a woman like you.
Oh, really?
I had no idea you've been
looking at me like that,
dirty boy!
I'm the dirty one?!
You've got your
boobs all over me!
Come on, Glenny-baby,
you're no fun.
[RUMIA]
There you are!
Oh, Professor Arfonia!
[CELICA]
What's wrong?
You need your teacher?
[RUMIA]
Yes, ma'am.
There's something
I wanted to ask him.
Really?
You need some help, huh?
Well I guess the great Glenn
Radars has a responsibility
to use his teaching
powers for good.
[SISTINE] I didn't want her
to ask, and this is why!
[RUMIA]
I thought his answer was great.
He's so easy to understand.
[SISTINE] When he tries, he's
an incredible magic teacher.
But he's still an idiot.
[RUMIA]
Hey, Sisti.
Remember when I first came here
and started living
with your family?
Why are you bringing that up?
It took us a while to get to
know each other, didn't it?
At first we didn't get along.
Yeah, that's true.
But now I can honestly say
you're my closest friend.
Maybe you and Professor Radars
will become close too.
[SISTINE]
That is so not happening!
[RUMIA laughs]
Are you blushing?
[EVIL MAGE 2A]
Is the plan proceeding smoothly?
[EVIL MAGE 2B]
Yes.
But there's the man Celica
Arfonia brought on board.
Goes by Glenn.
[EVIL MAGE 2A] He's some low
rent mage and no threat to us.
Proceed as planned when the
magic conference commences.
[EVIL MAGE 2B]
Understood.
I shall pray for
the plan's success.
All glory to the Divine Wisdom.
[GLENN yelling]
I'm late again!
[GLENN]
I know you're there.
Might as well come out.
[CARREL] It was quick little
barrier to ward people off.
Still...
I have to say you've
got pretty sharp eyes
for an amateur mage.
I don't know who you are,
but in case you didn't
hear my yelling, I'm late.
Lucky for you,
your itinerary's changed.
Your new destination
is the afterlife!
Corruption.
Fester!
[STUDENTS chattering]
You'd think he was
some kind of celebrity.
[RUMIA giggles]
Say it.
Are you worried you won't
get as much attention
now that he's popular?
What's that supposed to mean?!
Why would I care?!
[door slams]
Good morning, students.
Sorry we're late.
What is this? Who are you?
You're not with the school!
I'm afraid your teacher
has another engagement.
We're filling in.
[SISTINE]
You think we're stupid?
Outsiders are not allowed
inside the academy!
You need to leave right
now or I'll call security!
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Bang.
[STUDENTS gasp]
That's military-grade magic!
Mouth off to us again,
everyone dies.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
We're looking for someone.
Rumia is what she's
been calling herself.
If that's you,
then raise your hand.
Nobody?
That's strange, she's supposed
to be in this class.
Maybe you're Rumia?
No. It's not me.
Then do you know
this Rumia girl?
No, sir, I don't.
Are you sure?
There's nothing
I hate more than a liar.
[SISTINE]
What's this about?
What are you planning
to do with Rumia?
You're asking that
like you know her.
Why don't you just
answer my question?
I warned you once.
--Bye--
--[RUMIA] I'm Rumia.
Oh?
So you were right
here all along?
Yeah. We knew, of course.
I was just playing
a fun little game
where we'd kill all your
classmates until you fessed up.
Okay, that's enough
messing around.
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Yeah, yeah, fine.
[EVIL MAGE 2B]
Let's go.
No, Rumia, don't!
It's all right.
I'm sure Professor Radars
will come to the rescue
soon enough.
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
You mean your substitute?
We already killed that twerp.
--Liar!
--That can't be...
[EVIL MAGE 2B]
Now come.
[RUMIA]
What are you after?
Why are you taking me?
[EVIL MAGE 2B] You should know
perfectly well, Rumia Tingel.
Or should I say
Princess Ermiana?
You're supposed to be long gone,
and yet here you are.
A royal girl everyone
thinks is dead.
That makes you a rather
valuable card for us to play.
[SISTINE yells]
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Ya know, you're a pretty girl.
Be a waste not to enjoy you.
[SISTINE] I'm the daughter
of the proud house of Fibel!
That supposed to impress me?
I have a real eye for this,
and to be honest, having my way
with girls like Rumia isn't fun.
She may look weak,
but she's the type whose spirit
won't break no matter what.
You, on the other hand...
You're the opposite.
You act tough,
but you're just a child
hiding your weakness
behind a mask.
I enjoy breaking girls
like you most of all--
feeling you melt all around me.
Screw yourself!
I'll never submit to you!
[gasps]
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Huh?
[snickers]
What pretty skin you have.
[SISTINE]
Please. Stop.
What's that?
Just please, don't hurt me.
Please don't.
[EVIL MAGE 2C laughs]
You're breaking down already?
This is gonna be a blast!
[SISTINE]
No... Someone, save me!
Let's get this party started!
Hm?
Huh?
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Who the hell are you?
Sorry. I can leave.
[SISTINE]
Help, you idiot!
[GLENN sighs] Look, sock hat.
I get it, girls think
you're disgusting.
But this aint gonna change that.
Oh, no. Professor, get out!
First you tell me to help,
now you're tellin' me to leave.
Which is it?
[SISTINE] He's about to fire!
I'm saying get out of the way!
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Too late.
[SISTINE gasps]
Bang.
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Huh?
Bang! Bang!
[GLENN]
Your magic won't work anymore.
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
The Fool arcana?
[GLENN] By using the magic spell
that I've tied to this card,
I can completely seal off
the activation of all magic
within a set range, centered
around yours truly.
[GLENN]
That's my original spell.
It's called The Fool's World.
Your own original spell?
You're telling me a mage
like you is on that level?
[SISTINE] Sealing his enemy's
magic would make him invincible.
Heh. Of course, my spells
won't work either.
[SISTINE, EVIL MAGE 2C]
Uh?
[GLENN] I mean, obviously.
I'm in the effective range, too.
[EVIL MAGE 2C laughs]
How exactly is a mage
supposed to fight
if he seals his own magic?
You idiot!
[SISTINE]
We're done for!
[chuckles]
Get out before--
You! You're dead!
[EVIL MAGE 2C yells]
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
Huh?
That's the Imperial Army's
hand-to-hand combat style.
Just who the hell are you?
I'm Glenn Radars.
Substitute teacher.
But if you're still alive,
that means you defeated Carrel!
That's impossible.
Some mage who challenges
people to fist-fights
could never beat him.
[GLENN]
Good grief.
If you're that freaked
out by the whole
non-magic combat thing, I can
try to make you feel better.
I'll finish you with the
legendary super magical
iron fist Magical Punch!
Here goes!
Magical...
...Punch!
[chuckles]
[EVIL MAGE 2C]
That was a kick.
Well yeah, that's the part
that makes it magical.