[LELOUCH] The Knights of the
Round have become members
of the student council.
And while I still haven't
cleared that problem, what...
What were you saying?!
That Shirley and I were--
Yes. It's true, Shirley
and you were kissing.
Mm! Uh?!
Um, I wasn't wrong
in doing that, was I?
I was afraid she might
discover this control room,
so I thought that's what I
should do in your character.
Bad call.
You were mistaken there.
Sayoko! I've told you already!
You were acting too nice
as his stand-in!
No, hold on.
Aside from this,
she did a good job.
[ROLO]
Lelouch!
I know Sayoko used to be
in your service but...!
[SAYOKO]
Actually, to be precise,
I was working for
the Ashford family.
[ROLO]
I know that!
You were in charge of caring
for Nunnally, right?
[VILLETTA] I guess the problems
of the Knights of Round
will have to wait.
[SAYOKO] Master Lelouch, I have
your schedule for tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
[ROLO] Sayoko made promises
to other people
without considering all
the consequences.
[SAYOKO]
I was instructed to maintain
his interpersonal relationships.
[LELOUCH]
It can't be helped.
Quite careless for
a female ninja.
I am a secret service agent.
A 37th master of the
Shinozaki school--
[LELOUCH] Sayoko! Wha...
What's with this schedule?!
[SAYOKO] Allowing for
three hours of sleep,
you have dates scheduled
with 108 girls.
Fourteen of them are waiting
for cancellations,
and they've been on the
wait list for six months.
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu just did it so suddenly!
I wonder if I can say
we're going steady...
But I wasn't able
to talk to him today.
[SHIRLEY]
Prez!
Can I have a minute with you
when we go back to our room?
There's something I'd really
like to talk to you about.
Prez?
Huh?!
Oh, sorry, Shirley.
I didn't hear you.
[SHIRLEY]
No, it's okay. I just--
[GIRL A] I've got a date
with Lelouch tomorrow!
Huh?!
[GIRL B] Oh? I heard that
Giselle in class B said
that she'd go to the
art gallery with him.
[GIRL C] Yup! He's taking
me out, too, to a movie.
[GIRLS]
Me, too!
Lu... Lu...!
[SAYOKO] And that confirms
your schedule for today.
Since you have no
classes pending,
I was able to fill all 24 hours.
At 0700 hours, you'll enjoy
a homemade box lunch.
At 0900 hours, you'll
visit the art gallery.
At 1030 hours, shopping.
At 12 noon, a trip to
the aquarium, and from there
travel abroad aboard Shinkiro.
Please go underwater until you
are 400 kilometers from shore.
You'll change clothes inside
the cockpit and proceed
to the Chinese Federation, where
you'll conclude a trade treaty
in
You are allotted 47 minutes to
complete your business there,
then you'll return here to see
a late movie at 2100 hours.
At midnight 02, you'll meet your
next date for a live show,
and then...
He's late! [growls]
Sorry, Shirley.
I promise I'll make time later
to explain all this to you.
[ANYA] You can start by
explaining it to me.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Lady Anya!
There's something
I want to ask.
[LELOUCH] Don't tell me I have a
date with a Knight of the Round!
[ANYA]
Same Lelouch?
[LELOUCH]
Uh?
That's a picture of me
when I was still a prince
back in the homeland!
O-Of course not.
Remarkable likeness.
But you know I'm
only a commoner.
[GINO]
Lelouch, old man!
[LELOUCH]
Ah!
What?!
May I please go to your
chess games with you?
Only the underground
ones where you bet!
[RIVALZ] When I told him h
you gambled on your games,
he begged me to take him along.
[LELOUCH]
Rivalz... I swear, you're--!
[GIRLS scream]
Oh, brother, they never quit!
Just gimme a break, already!
[GROUPIE A]
He's running away!
[LELOUCH]
Don't go ruining my reputation!
I've got tickets for the
late show in my room!
If I break my commitment, then
my next date will-- Ah...!
Darn it, Sayoko!
Lelouch is too frail for
such a heavy schedule.
And what's up with
all these women?
It's sorta like a
mental problem
[LELOUCH grunting]
Who did that?! I said
I wasn't running away!
Uh?!
[LELOUCH gasps]
Shirley...!
So, what lucky girl do you
have a date with this time?
[LELOUCH]
Um, I uh...
[SHIRLEY] You not only
gamble, but you run around
with other girls, too?!
Ah! You're pathetic!
[LELOUCH]
Wait a minute! It's just--
Uh. I forgot. Here.
This is for not explaining
to you about it.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Oh, it's an apology? What,
you think you can fix what you
did by giving me
some silly thing?!
[LELOUCH]
You've got it all wrong!
I just wanted to apologize!
[SHIRLEY]
An apology?!
[LELOUCH]
This is not good. I'm clearly
doing something wrong and
don't know how to make it right.
Dammit, if only C.C.
was here to help me.
[MILLY]
Attention everyone!
I have decided on my
graduation event!
And I'm going to christen
it Cupid Day!
[GINO] That's swell, but isn't
it a bit early for graduation?
Well not for me. I'm
repeating my senior year.
I can graduate as soon as
I earn enough course credit.
[GINO] Oh... so that's how the
education system works here.
Prez, are you really planning
to graduate soon?
Why not wait and do it
with the rest of us?
Milly, my dear...
Madam President!
[GINO] This "Cupid Day" of
yours, what exactly is it?
[MILLY laughs]
You wanna know?
Meow.
On the appointed day,
I'll have every student
in school wearing
one of these hats.
The boys will get this color.
Then, if you steal the hat of
your target and put it on...
And then what?
[MILLY] By order of the student
council president, me,
those two will be proclaimed
boyfriend and girlfriend!
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?!
[GIRLS]
Wha...?!
[ODYSSEUS]
Hm... It's a bit rash, isn't it?
Declaring war on the
Chinese Federation?
[SCHNEIZEL] Hm, is that
what His Majesty said?
Yes. He told us
to take all of it.
[CARINE]
I agree!
I say take out the Chinese
Federation for good!
Those savages
humiliated Odysseus,
and we can never
forgive them for that.
Guinevere, I harbor no grudge
for the incident that occurred
with the empress.
[ODYSSEUS] The war with
the E.U. is ongoing,
and Area 11 is on
the path to peace,
so I'd prefer to
settle this without--
Oh, as if we care about
what Nunnally does there!
[ODYSSEUS] Carine,
Nunnally is around your age.
You should make an attempt
to be friends with her.
[GUINEVERE] This would be
an easy matter to solve
if Cornelia was present.
Bismark, have you
heard anything?
[BISMARK]
I haven't.
And she apparently hasn't
contacted Lord Guilford, either.
[GUINEVERE]
Then who will lead our troops?
[SCHNEIZEL]
We can station two divisions
along the Mongolian border.
Huh?
Are you offering to take
command, Prince Schneizel?
[SCHNEIZEL]
Battle is unnecessary.
The Chinese Federation
has fallen apart.
We can gain half their
territory by rattling sabers
and through negotiations.
Will that placate the emperor?
[EMPEROR] Oh? Is that
what Schneizel said?
[BISMARK] Yes, Your Majesty.
Do you approve?
[EMPEROR]
You, the Knight of One,
the mightiest knight of
the empire, asks me that?
[BISMARK] Your Majesty, war is
merely one method of diplomacy.
However, it's far and away
the least efficient of them.
Heh. Perhaps you're right.
War has historically been an
action favored by idiots.
[RESEARCHER groans]
I've finally grabbed it.
The tail of Geass!
And now I'll drag it
from the shadows.
I'll wipe away the stain
from Euphy's name at last!
[GUILFORD]
Princess... Where are you now?
[GINO] C'mon, Suzaku. It's
Milly's graduation event.
[SUZAKU] It's like I said
before. I'd really wanna go.
But unlike you and Anya,
I'm an aide to a viceroy,
so I just can't.
Meetings come first.
Jeez, you really need
to loosen up, my friend.
Say hi to my fiancé
for me, will you?
What? You're serious about that?
You should probably give her
a call after we're done here.
Huh?!
"Now" has a funny habit of
not waiting around forever.
Wow, what a surprise.
I never thought I'd hear you say
something like that, Guilford.
[GUILFORD]
Your rank may have changed,
but you did start out as
Princess Euphemia's knight.
As the knight of Princess
Cornelia, I'd like you to see
me as a source of advice that
you'll ask for when needed.
Well that's mature of you!
Anyway, can we get to the
main question at hand now?
It's about the Guren, which I
have taken into my care...
[KALLEN]
Took you long enough.
So, am I here for torture?
Or maybe execution?
Do what you want with me.
[NUNNALLY] I'll do nothing
like that to you.
It's been a such a long
time. Hello, Kallen.
[LELOUCH] At this rate,
it'll be impossible for me
to smash the world and
create a new one!
It's Cupid Day. I'm going
to end my relationship
with all the girls
at today's event.
[ROLO] Ah. That will leave
you free and in the clear.
[LELOUCH] Fortunately, we
were able to get the teachers
to participate in this, too.
Huh?
[LELOUCH] Villetta, you're going
to steal my hat from me.
But won't that just invite
weird misunderstandings?
I think Sayoko needs to
take responsibility here--
Sorry, but I can't help.
I have to play stand-in during
the event for Master Lelouch.
And we've got to make sure
that some strange
girl doesn't get it!
[VILLETTA]
Have Shirley grab the hat!
Yes, that's definitely
an option to consider.
That girl is completely
head-over-heels for you.
She did shoot me in order
to protect you, after all.
[LELOUCH]
That's why I don't want her
mixed up in this any further.
[ROLO]
Huh?
[MILLY]
Yes, that's right, Suzaku.
The rooftop garden's
finally finished.
Suppose I can't keep avoiding
the real world forever.
[SUZAKU]
I'm sorry.
I really hate missing
your graduation event.
[MILLY] I understand. You have
important work to do, right?
[SUZAKU]Um, y-yeah.
Then my final act for you is to
cast my special magic spell!
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
[MILLY] Relax! Ha, ha. You need
to unwind from time to time.
Thanks a lot Prez,
I appreciate it.
[MILLY]
See ya!
Now let's get this
show on the road.
[MILLY] Attention everyone!
This is Milly Ashford speaking
for the last time as student
council president!
My graduation event, Cupid
Day, is about to begin!
Oh, and before you start,
make sure you're at least two
meters away from your target.
[SHIRLEY] Lulu. I don't care
how hopeless you are...
No!
Since you are utterly hopeless,
it's up to me to salvage you!
[RIVALZ] Prez, you don't really
want to be engaged, do you?
Deep down, you want me
to steal you away. Right?
[MILLY] You should all be
familiar with the rules.
If you capture your
target's hat and put it on,
then you have to be
boyfriend and girlfriend!
I won't question how
you obtain the hat.
You're allowed to use
teams or tools, as well.
Now, before we begin,
I'll just say one thing.
Any club that brings me the
hat of Lelouch Lamperouge
in class 3-D gets their
budget increased ten-fold!
[LELOUCH]
What?!
Lulu's hat?!
Prez, why?!
[STUDENTS shouting]
Tsk! This is all
a horrible dream!
[MILLY]
All right! Let's do it!
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu wait--
[ROLO] Stopping this many people
at once is incredibly hard work!
Oops. Sorry 'bout that.
Now, move.
He's mine! [groans]
--[FEMALE E] Huh?!
--[SHIRLEY] Aagh!
He vanished!
Where'd he go?!
Sorry about this.
Forget it. We're good.
[BARTLEY]
H-H-Hold on.
Should that theory be accurate,
then we're the worst
criminals in all of history!
[LAB WORKER A]
Let's get out of here!
We're through fine-tuning
Jeremiah!
We'd be abandoning our nation!
[CORNELIA]
Freeze! My dear Bartley...
That voice...
Princess Cornelia?!
Why are you here, Bartley?
[BARTLEY] Thank heaven
you've come! Please save us!
[CORNELIA]
Hm?
[BARTLEY] We were ordered
to be here. By the emperor.
My father?
[BARTLEY]
The world is racing
down the path
towards destruction!
[CORNELIA]
Uh?!
[GINO laughs]
[GINO]
Follow me, ladies!
[GIRLS]
Lord Gino!
[LELOUCH]
I see.
It appears that Gino did come to
this school just to play around.
Anya seems suspicious
about my true identity,
but not enough to
prove troublesome.
The matter of the Knights of
the Round has been cleared.
Now, I've only to switch
places with Sayoko
and have her play along
with the Prez...
[MIYA] I did it! Now I get
to be Lelouch's girlfriend!
Of course.
Miya, right?
What's up, honey bunch?
[LELOUCH] Would you mind very
much... giving me that hat back?
[MIYA]
Okay.
So where should we switch?
Here will do.
Very well, then.
[MIYA] Hm? Whoa, now I'm
more confused than usual.
What am I doing here?
[MILLY]
Huh? Lelouch is gone?
[UNDERLING] Yeah, according
to the gardening club.
[RUGBY GUY]
Rugy team here!
Lelouch has been spotted
at point KT-01!
Yes...!
Alert all Ashford Academy club
members! Surround Lelouch
between the boy's dorms
and the central courtyard!
[RUGBY TEAM]
Sir! Yes, sir!
[SAYOKO]
Hm? Agh!
The rugby team's getting
that budget bonus, pal!
GO...!
[RUGBY TEAM yells]
[SAYOKO grunts]
[RUGBY GUY]
Huh?!
[SAYOKO]
Fair thee well!
Huh?
[LELOUCH] Sayoko!
Watch what you have me say!
Or I'll come off as
being kind of mental.
[SAYOKO]
Sorry, it was involuntary.
[LELOUCH] Just be careful.
And don't go to the rear gate.
Villetta's standing by there.
[SAYOKO]
Understood.
Lelouch is more
physical than normal.
[SAYOKO] I would like to let
you catch me, Miss Milly,
but at the moment...
Archery and equestrian clubs,
from the side of hall,
you can surround him!
Go on around the school
buildings to gym number two.
The science club will probably
be positioned dead ahead.
[SCIENCE CLUB A]
Fire!
[SCIENCE CLUB B]
No way!
Lelouch can't do
stuff like that!
[ROLO] If this keeps up, he
won't need my help after all.
[LELOUCH] Sayoko's overdoing it,
but that's how she operates.
There's no point
ordering her to stop.
Oh, well, she can take my place
in phys. ed from here on.
Glamour squad, move in!
[GLAMOUR GIRL A] After all,
Lelouch is a warm-blooded male.
[GLAMOUR GIRL B]
Yeah, we'll catch him off guard.
[SAYOKO] Using your bodies
against me is useless!
[GLAMOUR GIRLS]
Huh...?!
Wow, I'm sort of in shock!
[MALE STUDENT]
Where's Lelouch?!
[FEMALE D]
Where'd he go?!
[FEMALE B]
Nobody's caught him yet!
[MILLY]
Attention, all students!
If Vice President
Lelouch is spotted,
commence a simultaneous...
[SHIRLEY] Oh boy, the Prez is
in full-scale "play" mode.
Still... what's going on?
I thought Lulu was
completely hopeless
but now I'm finding out
he's a super athlete.
[STUDENT B]
Hey look, it's Shirley!
[FEMALE D]
We have to catch Lelouch!
[RIVALZ] Prez! If Lelouch
is who you want,
then I, Rivalz Cardemonde,
will give you what you want!
My best friend in the world!
Uh. Huh? Whoa, that
can't be for real...!
It is.
[SUZAKU] The Mordred's
just been launched?!
[GUILFORD]
It's the Black Knights then?!
[ANNOUNCER] Emergency dispatch
from the government bureau!
Defcon 2! Defcon 2!
A riot has erupted in
the school district!
Knight police SWAT unit,
prepare to move out!
[LELOUCH] Uh! I should have
guessed that Anya doesn't
possess a grain of
common sense, either!
Take the operation into final
phase! Sayoko, to the library!
Oh, there.
Hm...
This is the spot where
Lulu was acting strange.
I wonder...
[SAYOKO]
Shirley... Why now all times?
[ANYA]
Heat sources. Two places.
But which one is Lelouch?
[SHIRLEY]
Hm?
[gasps]
Watch out!
[LELOUCH grunts]
[SHIRLEY screams]
Twin Lelouches?
[VILLETTA]
Knight of Six, my lady!
This is an operations
area of the O.S.I.!
Please, withdraw your
Knightmare at once!
[ANYA]
This is wrong?
[VILLETTA]
Yes, very wrong.
[ANYA]
Wrong.
[SHIRLEY]
Say, Lulu...
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[SHIRLEY]
Why did you kiss me before?
Well, um, because...
...I like you.
[SHIRLEY] That's a lie,
I know you aren't serious.
Wrong!
[SHIRLEY]
Uh?
[LELOUCH]
I mean... I just...
A good question.
[SHIRLEY laughs]
So, you wanna do
more than just kiss?
Huh?!
It's okay, even if
you're not serious.
Uh! You shouldn't
speak that way!
Welcome back, Lulu.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[SHIRLEY] You haven't been
yourself lately, you know.
[SHIRLEY]
It's okay. I forgive you.
In return, close
your eyes for me.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[SHIRLEY]
Hurry up.
[LELOUCH]
O-Okay.
[LELOUCH grunts]
You thought I was gonna
give you a smooch?
Um, well, ya know... I thought
there was a possibility...
Oh, you dirty boy!
[LELOUCH]
No, it's just...!
Even so, I wanna
try and make you
fall in love with me
for real, some day.
[LELOUCH]
Uh...
I told you.
I said love is power.
I can see you guys still have
a lot to learn around here,
don't you?
This is a school for commoners.
Things like this take
place all the time!
[STUDENT C]
Look at that!
[FEMALE F] How disappointing,
but I'm not surprised.
I guess that's
the end of game.
Butit might have meant little
more this time around.
[MILLY]
Huh?
Yeah. Maybe It did...
...a bit.
What in the world was
all that uproar about?
Sorry, sir.
It looks like it was the
president's graduation event.
[VILLETTA]
It's unusual to say the least
that he would change
plans like that.
[ANYA]
Changed plans?
Uh, I meant she.
Shirley's plan apparently
worked out quite well.
[MILLY]
Lelouch!
Looks like you
finally understand.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
You mean you did this for us?
Cause you two really
wear on my patience.
Don't ever hesitate, your
student days coming to an end.
Uh! Prez, are... you
really graduating?
[MILLY]
Mm-hm!
Hey, Prez!
What is it?
Thank you for everything
you've done here at school.
Uh.
[FEMALE D] The last three
years were so much fun!
[FEMALE C] You were
the best president ever!
[FEMALE B]
Thank you!
[SUZAKU]
Madame president!
Congratulations on
graduating from Ashford.
[MILLY]
Mm-hm. And with that,
this girl is no longer
avoiding real world!
[STUDENTS cheer]
Hello, everyone! How are you?
My name's Milly Ashford!
Beginning today, I'll
be your go-to-girl
for weather information
here on the weather corner!
Let's start with an update...
[RIVALZ] From student council
president to a weather reporter.
[ROLO]
How'd she qualify?
I heard she chose a talent
agency while still in school.
[GINO]
Hmm...
[ANYA]
She's from nobility.
[RIVALZ]
She said she never likes
to do anything halfway, so...
[ROLO] Then why'd she
call off her engagement?
Did she have to?
[GINO] Wow, Lloyd must
be in a state of shock!
[laughs] Just what I'd expect
from my former fiance.
Lloyd doesn't seem
upset about it.
It's all bravado.
No, the man never wanted to
get married in the first place.
[MILLY]
You see, Nina?
I'm trying to face
who I really am.
[SHIRLEY]
Yeah, I saw her on TV.
Typical Prez, huh?
So, what do you think we ought
to do with the rooftop garden?
Right. Well then, I'll bring
back some herb seedlings
from the store.
Would you talk
to the gardening club, Lulu?
Okay, see ya later!
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?!
[V.V.] This is the
eighth area, correct?
[JEREMIAH] Yes. But the people
who were affected by the Geass
power have been deployed as
secret police, haven't they?
We don't know, so we're
cleaning up the situation.
You've been given
a Geass Canceller,
which can destroy all types
of Geass power. Therefore...
Yes, I understand.
We don't know who's under
the influence of Geass.
However, once I'm done
with Ashford Academy,
I'll take care of old
business with Lelouch.
[SHIRLEY]
I'm remembering now...
I remember Zero, and the
one who killed my father...
It's Lelouch!
[LELOUCH] I must give
Japan its independence.
And at the same time,
I have to put together a
dating itinerary with Shirley.
There are 18
hypothetical routes.
I've set up a way
for C.C. and Kaguya
to send me emergency messages.
I may even get the chance
to work out rescue
preparations for Kallen.
But I have no idea
what Shirley will like.
What should I do? Is there
someone I can consult?
I get the feeling that I'm going
to make the wrong choices again.
That worries me to no end!