[MED. OFFICIAL 1] About this
specially administrated
zone of Japan...
There is some unpleasant rumors
about Princess Euphemia.
[VICE MINISTER] It must be due
to the Kamine Island matter.
You think she
contacted Zero there?
[MINISTRY 2] I suspect
there's a connection here
that goes all the way to top.
No connection.
The viceroy wasn't the only one
asking what was going on.
But in any case, our connections
with them need to be...
Mm, right, we'll have
to sever ties at once.
I'm afraid it's too late.
--[GROUP gasps]
--[VICE MINISTER] Uh?!
All the evidence has already
been gathered, Vice-Minister.
Namely, that NAC
profit-sharing bribe.
I appreciate this,
General Darlton.
With this...
With this, we can finally
sweep away the parasites
who were sucking
Prince Clovis dry.
[chuckles] There are
more rats than expected.
And all of them are confused by
Princess Euphemia's proposed
special zone, aren't they?
[SUZAKU]
Over two hundred thousand people
have applied to join
the Japan special zone.
The way things look, that
number's only going to grow.
Thanks to you, Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
Huh?
Because of what you represent
to the Japanese people,
everyone is rallying.
They believe in what
we're doing here.
No, you're giving me
too much credit.
It must be due to your
proclamation, Princess.
I'm truly thankful
for this. I really am.
Just as I'm thankful to you.
And I hope that you're going
to help me with everything
that's still to come.
--Yes, Your--
--Not like that...
Yes.
[EUPHEMIA giggles]
[NEWS WOMAN] The specially
administrated zone of Japan
is the first attempt
of its kind in Britannia,
and was personally proposed by
Her Highness, Princess Euphemia.
This youthful inspiration was
an idea from her school years.
It has not only caught
the Homeland's attention,
--but tomorrow's inaugural
--If Princess Euphemia
--ceremony will be
--thinks it's a good idea,
--broadcast worldwide.
--then even I have to...
The NAC, lead by
Kirihara Industries,
gives its wholehearted
support to the plan.
[SCHNEIZEL] Euphy really
is amazing, isn't she?
Now the terrorist
groups in Area 11
will lose their popular
support and fall apart.
Public order will be stabilized.
I personally oppose this.
[SCHNEIZEL] But, since you
understand the situation,
you've sent Darlton to
advise her, have you not?
To ensure public policy
stays on track.
It's a measure that a viceroy
would obviously take.
[SCHNEIZEL]
Hm.
Did you approve
her future plans
as the viceroy or
as her older sister?
[CORNELIA grunts]
The Japan special zone
doesn't sound that bad.
[KUBOUIN]
A shadow of Japan
that's given to us out
of pity is worthless.
We were granted this
concession by the Britannians
as a result of our
resistance efforts.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Lord Kirihara!
I heard a rumor
that you'll be given
a favored position
in the special zone
in exchange for the
Sakuradite mining rights.
[KIRIHARA]
Don't be suspicious.
It's merely a request
to join the ceremony.
[KUBOUIN]
That's a clever excuse.
[KIRIHARA]
How dare you!
Zero.
What about him and all
of the Black Knights?
[TOHDOH]
The situation is serious.
It's not only supporters.
Some of the members
within our own ranks
have already applied to
join the special zone.
Unlike the Black Knights,
there's no risk involved
in signing up for the
Japan special zone.
Besides, when you compare
the pedigreed princess
with the mysterious
unknown man behind the mask,
it's obvious which one
exudes more appeal.
[MINAMI]
There's a rumor that
Kyoto's cooperating
with them, too.
[TAMAKI]
What's up with that?!
They're offering
equality, that's why.
Equality, my ass!
Don't just accept
their word for it!
I agree.
[KALLEN]
Mm?
[ASAHINA]
But unless we decide
how to respond to
this quickly...
[OHGI] You want to apply
to the special zone?
[VILLETTA] Because there it
won't make any difference
who's a Britannian
and who's an Eleven.
[OHGI]
Listen--
If it works like
Euphemia's proposal,
then it wouldn't be wrong
for the Black Knights
to support this, right?
Yeah, sure, like Britannians
would ever honor a promise!
I think we should
support the zone.
It doesn't contradict
what Zero said, does it?
But Ohgi, that's--
First off, if we accept
peace on their terms,
we'll be forced to disarm.
That is a problem, isn't it?
We would also get
swallowed up in their regime
and lose our independence.
[DIETHARD] On the other hand,
if we don't support it,
then we're against
equality and freedom.
[OHGI]
Then let's support it!
What, without any
guarantees in place?
[OHGI]
But we can't ignore it, either!
[LELOUCH] Sorry about having
you drop me off like this.
Hey, you helped me go
shopping after all.
Besides, I heard that you were
gonna go meet up with Shirley.
She might need me
to go shopping, too.
Britannians shouldn't be worried
just because of the
special zone starting up.
Oh, yeah, I think
you're right about that.
Anyway, you'd better make up
with Shirley pretty soon, buddy.
[NOBLEMAN] I don't care
about your "special zone"!
--I don't care about "support"!
--[KID groaning]
--I'd sooner die than sign that!
It's a Nobleman, a
shining example of class.
[NOBLEMAN] You think
you're equal to us now?!
The lower classes should
simply obey their betters
without any backtalk!
--[footsteps]
--[LELOUCH] There it is.
That's the true nature of the
sub-viceroy's "benevolence."
[NOBLEMAN]
What do you want?
Doesn't it feel good to
look down from above?
It is rather like being a god.
Hold it, school boy.
Just back off.
[LELOUCH] I think you
should go home right now.
Yeah, okay, I will.
Well, I'd better get going.
[NOBLEMAN] Huh? What
did you say to him?!
Come back here at once!
[LELOUCH]
What's wrong, Sir Nobleman?
Confusing borrowed power
with your own ability
is a big mistake, you know.
Garbage like you
should simply die
and be thrown out where no--
All right, already,
let's break this up!
Mister, why don't you
apologize? Whaddya say?
Apologize?! You insolent whelp!
Go away!
[NOBLEMAN]
Uh... Hmph!
[KID]
Um... Thank you very much.
[LELOUCH]
It was nothing.
[SHIRLEY] He came to
the aid of that Eleven,
even though he's Zero!
Or because he's Zero!
So, why would he have been
talking to Princess Euphemia?
Stop it.
If I dig too deep,
it'll be dangerous.
[DARLTON]
The NAC...
Or rather, Kyoto, as it's
known among the terrorists.
Tomorrow, after the ceremony,
why don't you dissolve your
group and leave Mt. Fuji?
We can talk about
a legal agreement
if you hand over the mining
operation to us peacefully.
[KIRIHARA]
Uh...
[DARLTON] Of course,
that will mean the end
of your support to
the Black Knights.
Whether Zero comes tomorrow
or not doesn't matter.
With this, that man's
downfall is assured.
[LELOUCH chuckles]
--[NUNNALLY] Hm?
--[LELOUCH] I'm back.
Hello, Lelouch. Welcome home.
Oh, where's Shirley?
I'm sorry, Nunnally,
she never showed up.
I wasn't able to get
a hold of her, either.
More of her getting
back at you, huh?
Well, you have seemed
sort of chilly toward her.
You think so?
Then I'll be nicer.
Um, Sayoko, would you
bring us some tea, please?
Yes. As you wish, my lord.
I get the feeling you're worried
about something, Lelouch.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[NUNNALLY]
Does it involve Euphy?
It'd be selfish to say that
I want to see her again.
I'd like to, I admit it,
but that would simply cause
trouble for you both.
[LELOUCH]
You like Euphy, don't you?
[NUNNALLY]
Yes, very much.
The same way you like her.
[LELOUCH]
Yeah... I did like her.
[REPORTER] We're bringing you
live coverage from the stadium
where the inaugural
ceremony will be held
for the specially
administrated zone of Japan.
The place is already
packed full with Elevens--
Sorry, I mean with Japanese--
and those unable to get in are
gathered outside the stadium.
[REPORTER 2] Leslie, do you
think Zero will show up here?
[LESLIE] No, and we've heard
nothing about it at this time.
[HIGH OFFICIAL chuckles]
Will Zero even show up?
I seriously doubt it.
What do you think?
[E.U. CHAIRMAN] If the data
we have on the man is accurate,
then I don't believe
he will, either.
Princess Euphemia, it's time.
Right.
[STADIUM gasping, chattering]
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
Huh?
Zero!
[MAN 1]
It's Zero!
[MAN 2]
Zero is here!
Oh! He came after all!
You accept that you've lost?
[KIRIHARA]
What are you doing?!
I thought I would have
to carry your identity
with me to the grave!
If people discover that
Zero is a Britannian prince,
it's all over!
They'll mistake this for a
farce planned by the Empire!
That would even cause
the specially administrated
zone to fall apart!
[CAPTAIN]
Your target is Zero.
If he makes any suspicious
moves, kill him at once.
[MEN]
Yes, my lord.
[EUPHEMIA] Zero! Welcome to the
specially administrated zone!
[ZERO] Greetings,
Euphemia li Britannia!
I wish to request an
audience with you!
Just with me?
[ZERO]
Yes, with you alone!
[LESLIE] Something
major has happened here,
ladies and gentlemen!
Zero has just
appeared in the open!
Under Princess
Euphemia's direction,
he is moving toward the G1.
[CECILE] I'm afraid
something's going to happen.
We should have gone
there like I thought.
[LLOYD]
What for?
It's not as if we had
choice in the matter.
Everyone said that if
Lancelot was there waiting,
Zero wouldn't show.
[BODYGUARD 1] It appears
to be safe, Your Highness.
Then this way, please.
Princess Euphemia,
it's too dangerous
to be alone with this man.
As your knight,
I request that you allow me
to accompany you to safety!
No, it's all right.
Please, just trust me, Suzaku.
[TAMAKI]
C'mon...
How long are we supposed
to hang around here?
What, it's not enough for you
that Zero instructed
us to wait here?
Yeah, whatever...
Well, first of all,
we have to confirm the
empire's true intentions.
[TOHDOH]
Deputy-commander?
Uh-- Yes.
[TOHDOH] Zero knows
their real intentions.
Isn't that why
he told us to hide
and wait in all four directions?
[OHGI]
A risky assumption!
[TOHDOH] He's even got Diethard
and Rakshata standing by.
Zero is probably planning
to assassinate Euphemia.
[EUPHEMIA] Even though
the cameras are off,
you're still being
extremely careful, aren't you?
[ZERO] I've been in
hiding for a long time
due to a certain
empire, I'm afraid.
This is a needle gun made
from ceramic and bamboo.
It can't be picked up
on a metal detector.
Lelouch, you would never
shoot me, would you?
No... I would never do that.
You'll be doin' the
shooting, Euphy.
Huh?!
Is this really all right,
leaving her alone with Zero?
But she ordered us to.
[BODYGUARD 2]
Well, she can always press
the emergency call button.
[SUZAKU gasps]
--[BODYGUARD 3] Hm?
--Is there something wrong?
Why are you here?
What are you doing with Zero?
[C.C.]
It looks like he can see me.
Is that because of
our indirect contact
and what occurred
at Kamine Island?
Or is it because he--
But if that's the case, then...
[LELOUCH] This ceremony
is being broadcast globally
and the world is
going to witness you,
a Britannian princess,
shoot Zero.
What do you think
will happen next?
Rioting would
break out, I imagine.
[LELOUCH]
Right.
Zero will become a martyr,
tricked into a deathtrap,
and instantly, your popularity
will crash to Earth.
What kind of nonsense
are you saying?
You should just help
me to rebuild Japan.
[LELOUCH] If you force
it upon us from on high,
then you're as bad
as Clovis was!
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
[LELOUCH] All tasks at
hand have been cleared.
After hovering near death,
Zero will be met with cheers
when he makes a
miraculous recovery.
Because people don't
give a damn about reason,
but nobody can resist miracles.
Now, take the gun.
Huh...?
There can only be one
messiah, you understand.
And when the people realize that
you're a false one,
they'll-- Ugh!
I-- I thought so.
I need to know one thing.
Are you the-- [groans]
[LELOUCH groaning]
[C.C. groans]
No... He's reached
that... point...!
[SUZAKU]
Hey! What's wrong?!
[gasps]
[SUZAKU gasps, groans]
[BODYGUARD 3]
Major Kururugi!
[BODYGUARD 2] Why you...!
What have you done to him?!
[BODYGUARDS scream]
[EUPHEMIA]
Lelouch!
--[gasps]
--[LELOUCH] Stop it!
Stop giving me your pity!
Spare me your charity!
This is something I have
to achieve on my own!
And so for that, I shall now
stain your hands with blood,
Euphemia li Britannia!
That isn't my name!
I've renounced it!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[EUPHEMIA] There'll probably
be a formal announcement
issued by the Homeland
about it any day now,
but I've given up my
claim to the throne!
But why?
It isn't because you
accepted Zero, is it?
Well, of course.
I have to pay the price for
doing something so selfish.
Those are the consequences.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Yes, but it wasn't difficult for
you to give that up, was it?
And I suppose you
did it for my sake.
[EUPHEMIA giggles]
As conceited as you ever were.
But no, I did it for Nunnally.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[EUPHEMIA]
She told me herself.
"All I want to is to
be with my brother.
and that's all that matters;
I want nothing more."
For that petty reason?
That's right, Lelouch.
That's how I made up my mind.
It made me stop and
seriously reflect on
what was truly
important to me in life.
Do you understand now?
I'm not giving up anything
that has significant
meaning or real worth to me.
And you don't need to worry.
I won't tell anyone about you.
[LELOUCH]
Hmph.
[chuckles]
And Cornelia?
It's not like we'll never
see each other again.
Euphy, you are a fool.
An amazing fool.
[EUPHEMIA] I know I'm not
as smart as you, Lelouch.
I've never been able to beat you
at games or studies, however--
However...
In your usual rash
"Euphy" fashion,
you've managed to end
up winning all of it.
When I think of you,
I don't visualize
a sub-viceroy or a princess.
I only see the plain little
Euphy who you used to be.
Then will you join plain
little Euphy and help her?
[LELOUCH grunts]
You are...
You are the worst opponent
I have ever faced.
[chuckles]
You win.
[EUPHEMIA]
Huh?
[LELOUCH] I'll amend my plans
to help out your special zone.
--[EUPHEMIA giggles]
--[LELOUCH] Ah.
But not as your
subordinate, all right?
All right!
Though you haven't got very
much faith in me, have you?
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[EUPHEMIA]
Did you honestly believe that
by simply threatening
me, I would shoot you?
Oh, no. You've got it all wrong.
When I really want people
to follow my orders,
they will not resist me.
Whether it's to shoot me,
to grant pardon to Suzaku,
or... any order at all.
[EUPHEMIA]
Oh, now you're being silly.
Stop playing with me.
[LELOUCH]
I'm serious!
For example, if I told you
to kill all the Japanese,
it wouldn't matter
how you felt about it.
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
No! Don't make me do it, please!
--I'm not...!
--[LELOUCH gasps]
Not going to do it... Please!
I don't want to kill them!
--[EUPHEMIA] No...!
--[LELOUCH] Did I...?!
[EUPHEMIA gasps]
You're right.
I have to kill all the Japanese.
[LELOUCH]
I've become like Mao!
I can't control my Geass power!
[LELOUCH] Forget the
order I just gave you!
Euphy!
Wait, Euphy! Don't!
[SCHNEIZEL]
Right.
I've reached an agreement
with the Chinese Federation,
therefore I should be returning
to the Homeland today.
Should we keep the
experimental subject
here then, Your Highness?
[SCHNEIZEL]
Yes. How intelligent is he?
Our resources are
rather limited in Area 11.
[SCHNEIZEL]
I see.
We should ask the Rosenberg
Institute about that.
Very well, I'll
arrange it with them
for you to send over
the experimental subject.
[BARTLEY]
Understood.
Then, what do we do with
the ruins on Kamine Island?
We have to wait to do anything
until the security situation in
Area 11 has been stabilized.
We can thank the specially
administrated zone for that.
Owing to Euphemia, everything's
going to work out perfectly.
Sub-viceroy, where's Zero?
[EUPHEMIA] Those of you who
call yourselves Japanese,
I have a favor to ask!
Could you all die, please?
--[WOMAN] Huh?!
--[MAN] What did she just say?
--[MAN 2] What the hell?!
--[CROWD chattering]
[ZERO]
Suzaku!
[ZERO] He's only
unconscious. But why?!
[EUPHEMIA]
Umm...
I was hoping you'd all
just commit suicide,
but you can't, can you?
Okay, soldiers, please
kill the Japanese!
Kill them all!
Ah! The woman's mad!
Cut the mics and cameras now!
[ZERO]
Euphy, no!
[SOLDIER 1]
Halt!
[ZERO]
Out of my way!
[SOLDIER 2]
Terrorist!
--[ZERO] Stand aside!
--[gunshot]
[OLD WOMAN screams]
Go on, soldiers, do
your duty! Hurry up!
[DARLTON]
Princess Euphemia!
What on earth's come over you?!
Please stop this at
once, Your Highness!
--This is--
--[gunshot]
[DARLTON groans]
General!
[ZERO gasps]
Forgive me, General,
but I mustn't let anyone
stand in my way.
I have to kill all the Japanese.
Now Britannians,
kill the Japanese!
[SUZAKU groans]
--[gunshots]
--[screaming]
[COMM 1] Kill the Elevens! All
troops, exterminate the Elevens!
[COMM 2] Don't let any
escape! Kill 'em all!
[SUZAKU]
Stop! What are you doing?!
All forces, this is
Suzaku Kururugi,
Knight of Honor of Britannia!
Cease fire at once!
[PILOT] We've been ordered to
kill all the Japanese here.
Princess Euphemia issued
the command herself.
[SUZAKU]
What?! Princess Euphemia did?!
No, that's absurd!
[PILOT]
You're Japanese, aren't you?
[SUZAKU gasps]
[MAN 1]
What's going on?!
[WOMAN 1]
What happened in there?!
[MAN 3]
It can't be.
--What does the TV say?
--[WOMAN 2] They cut the feed!
[ZERO]
Euphy, stop!
This thing...
My Geass did this?!
[OLD WOMAN 2]
Z-Zero...
Please help us...
You must help.
You're Japan's savior...
[ZERO]
Stop it...
Don't call me your savior.
Because I'm not the
messiah of Japan!
Zero, you're...
You're our only hope...
Stop it.
Don't... Don't force me...
Must I atone for this sin?
Is this a cross I
have to bear, too?!
[DARLTON groans]
Zero! You son of a bitch!
What did you do to Princess
Euphemia?! Tell me!
[ZERO]
Andreas Darlton...
...the closest of Cornelia's
inner circle advisors.
Tamaki, what's happening
inside the stadium?!
[TAMAKI] We're trying
to figure that out!
We're getting a feed
from the stadium now.
It appears--
Why can't you cut it off?!
We're not transmitting
this, it's someone else.
Stop it! It's going out
live to the entire world!
[DIETHARD] They will cut off
the broadcast at any minute now.
Let's upload the
data to the net.
You heard him.
Right.
[ADJUTANT 1]
Sir! C.C. has made contact
with the supreme commander!
Perfect! That clears up
our last problem, then.
[DIETHARD] I have no idea how
you arranged the situation,
but your scheme has gone well
beyond what I had expected.
[DARLTON groans]
[LELOUCH grunts]
[C.C.] I'm shocked. I didn't
think you'd go this far.
[LELOUCH]
It wasn't me.
What?! [gasps]
This time, I didn't
use the power.
Or I should say, I didn't
mean to use my Geass.
[C.C.]
I see...
Then what I felt earlier was...
I knew there were risks
when we made our contract.
You told me how dangerous
this power could be.
Nonetheless...!
[EMPEROR cackling]
Yes! You're worthy of
being called my child now!
[SCHNEIZEL gasps]
What madness is this?!
[BABY crying]
[GUILFORD]
Princess Cornelia, wait!
Don't follow me unless
you wanna come along!
[SUZAKU]
Euphy!
Have you located her
yet? Where is she?!
[CECILE]
I don't know!
We haven't been able to contact
General Darlton, either!
[MUNAKATA]
Something's dreadfully wrong.
Euphemia would never
do such a thing.
[OSAKABE] I wish there was
room to negotiate here,
but we can't be connected
to Kirihara now!
[KUBOUIN] Mm. We need
to save ourselves first.
Yes, and the "souvenir,"
is it ready?
[KAGUYA]
How pathetic.
[GROUP]
Hm?
Your survival is all
that counts in all of this?
My Lady, you really
shouldn't speak like that.
We need to survive for
the sake of Japan as well.
But then what's the point
if we're all that's left?
Watch your tongue, Kaguya!
You're just a girl
with family rank!
What purpose is having
Kyoto if we don't act now?!
[SUZAKU] I can't believe Euphy
would order the slaughter
of all those innocent people!
I've got to find her,
no matter what!
[WOMAN 3]
Huh?
[PEOPLE scream]
Hey! The Britannian forces have
begun moving out of the stadium!
[ZERO]
Right.
In this case, our only option is
to exploit Euphemia
to the utmost.
It's the... least we can do...
[C.C. sighs]
[gasps]
[PILOT 2]
Attention, Zero!
Return that unit! It's
property of our military-- Ah!
[ZERO] This is my order
to all Black Knights!
Euphemia has become our enemy!
The specially
administrated zone of Japan
is a cowardly trap
designed to lure us in!
All armored autonomous
battle knight units,
advance on the ceremony
grounds and wage an attack!
Wipe out all Britannian forces!
Save the Japanese! Hurry!
I have to!
I must find Euphy!
[LELOUCH]
Find her and kill her!
Who is the one responsible
for creating this situation?
Who is the one to bear the
sin for this grotesque tragedy?
Who is the one craving
for this battle?
And who is the one who
possesses the world?
Yes. I understand.
But, even so...
Even so, I...!