[C.C.]
The young Britannian Lelouch
vowed to avenge his mother
who was killed 8 years ago,
and he pledged to create a
world where his younger sister,
Nunnally, could find happiness.
For that purpose, he gained
power from a mysterious girl
named C.C., the power of
Geass, the absolute ability
to compel any person to
do whatever he commands.
Lelouch used this power to
embark on a path of destruction
aimed at the heart of
the Holy Britannian Empire
ruled by his father...
But at the end of that path,
what will he have gained?
And what will he have lost?
Geass is called the
power of the king,
yet of this power,
only one thing is clear:
those who use it walk
a path of solitude.
[EMPEROR]
It's been a long time, Lelouch.
My prodigal son.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH] Answer my
question about 8 years ago!
Why didn't you try
to protect mother?!
You knew the others
were plotting against her!
You knew everything!
[EMPEROR]
People are not equal.
[LELOUCH]
What?!
[EMPEROR] You have a
unique form of Geass,
a power that no one
else possesses.
Use it to get the
answer from me!
[LELOUCH]
He's baiting me,
trying to get me to
use my Geass on him.
But, if I look into his eyes,
then he'll look into mine!
His Geass requires eye contact,
just like mine does...
So the moment I look,
his Geass will take control
of me and he'll alter my
memories! What do I do?!
[EMPEROR]
What's wrong?
Are you not my son,
a prince of Britannia?
[LELOUCH] I have no time
to make the wrong choice!
These orders are from Zero!
Search through all
facilities! Obey Zero!
Bring all corpses to
the designated area.
We must determine if any of
the experimental soldiers
are among them.
But this is... a massacre!
[JEREMIAH]
Bartley, I hated you
for reconstructing
me with this body.
But your loyalty to the
imperial family was genuine.
So be it.
I make my final decision!
I will respect you!
Lelouch vi Britannia
commands you!
And now, die!
[EMPEROR growls]
[EMPEROR]
Very well, then.
I won.
[LELOUCH]
Nunnally... Mother...
I, uh... I did it.
[yells]
I don't knowbout Lelouch!
How many times must I say it?!
Would you swear to it
solemnly, on Shirley's grave?
[KALLEN]
Uh.
[KALLEN groans]
[SUZAKU] Now, you're going
to tell me everything.
With the help of this Refrain!
[KALLEN]
Don't. Please, don't! Stop it!
[SUZAKU]
You don't have to be afraid.
You'll lose your
will-power soon,
and then you'll answer
all my questions.
[KALLEN whimpers]
Brother, help me...
Now, you will obey my commands.
[SUZAKU grunting]
I will not... be like him...
[C.C.] How many years
has it been since we were
together face to face, V.V.?
In the end, I couldn't run
away from my destiny, could I?
Now I bear the burden
of... that destiny...
Huh?
[V.V.]
Of immortality...
[C.C.]
What? V.V., are you...?
[V.V.]
So, please, Charles...
Well, do you swear it?
[EMPEROR] Yes. In this
world full of lies...
We will never
lie to each other.
That's because I... I am
your... your big brother...
[LELOUCH]
I killed him. It was so easy.
I had questions for him.
Deaths he should have
answered for, but now...
[EMPEROR]
Oh? Whose?
You're impudent, Lelouch!
You're alive?!
That's impossible!
That bullet went
through your heart!
[EMPEROR]
Plots and schemes, deceptions.
You really thought
you could defeat me
with those cheap tricks?
You want the
power of a king?
Then have the courage
to come at me like a king!
[LELOUCH grunts]
Die!
[EMPEROR] You think that's
how a king does it?
[gasps] My Geass isn't working!
You still do not understand?
I am beyond the power
of guns or swords now!
No matter how you
attack me, it's useless!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[C.C.] Charles, why
steal V.V.'s Code now?
Why would you kill the older
brother you loved so much?
V.V. You loved
Marianne, didn't you?
[LELOUCH grunts]
[LELOUCH]
He's become immortal, too?!
I can't win.
There's no way I can win!
[EMPEROR] I've gained a new
power in place of Geass.
A power that goes far beyond.
And so, Lelouch, behold
and I shall show you
the true nature of this world!
What is this?!
Chigusa.
[VILLETTA] That was the name you
called me when I lost my memory.
What's my real name?
Villetta.
But that doesn't
change anything.
[VILLETTA]
I'm a Britannian baroness.
No matter what the reason,
if I don't erase the disgrace
of my having loved an Eleven,
I won't be able to
live in this world.
[OHGI]
Hmph. I suppose not.
If I must die, I just wish
it could've been in Japan.
[VILLETTA] You came here
knowing I was going to kill you?
Everybody dies. I wanted
to choose the time.
[VILLETTA] You can also
killed me if you want.
Tell me!
Why did a terrorist save a
Britannian in the first place?!
[OHGI]
In the beginning,
I thought I could get
information from you about Zero.
I tricked you, kept you
under surveillance.
But, while we lived together--
I'm your sworn enemy!
[OHGI]
But I still love you!
Are you insane?!
I must be. You are the enemy.
But I can't stop myself
from loving you!
[VILLETTA whimpers]
I wish I'd never
set eyes on you!
--[rustling]
--Uh?!
Uh? From intelligence?
[LELOUCH] What is Geass?!
I want the truth?!
[EMPEROR] How strange.
A child who's wrapped himself
in lies desires the
truth from others.
What?
[EMPEROR] The false name
and false mask of Zero,
what has it gotten you?
Everything! It got
me all the things
that ordinary people
can never obtain!
Followers! Territory!
[MASK 1]
You lost Euphemia.
[LELOUCH gasps]
[MASK 2] Suzaku and Nunnally
are also lost to your lies!
[LELOUCH] Shut up!
I did what I had to do!
People lie to survive!
No one is blameless!
[MASK 3] You want others
to know your true self,
yet you only show
them a false face.
[MASK 4] How can anyone know you
if you don't reveal yourself?
[MASK 5]
If you hide behind masks.
[MASK 6] You are afraid
that they'll find out
who you really are.
[LELOUCH]
No!
[EMPEROR] In the end,
your lies serve no purpose.
Because you are me and I
am you. All else is illusion.
Though there be worlds without
end, there is but one being.
In the past. In the future.
And now. Only one.
[LELOUCH]
One...? What are you saying?
[C.C.]
Charles.
Play time is over now.
There's nothing
in it for me now;
no value in the games anymore.
C.C.?
[C.C.] You don't have to cajole
him like this to get me here.
I already exist
in this realm.
[EMPEROR]
True enough, C.C. In that case,
I shall grant your wish.
You know what C.C.'s wish is?!
[C.C.]
Lelouch. It's time you knew
the conditions of our contract.
And what I desire.
My wish is to die. To end my
existence in all worlds forever.
But why? Why would
you want to die?!
[C.C.]
In the final stage of Geass,
the user attains the position
of the one who granted them
the power. Thus, you have
gained the power to kill me.
[LELOUCH]
Kill you? C.C...
[C.C.] Of all those I
made contracts with,
none has ever
reached that point.
But now there's Charles.
He has done it.
You mean... you made
your contract with me
so that you could
cease to exist?!
[C.C.]
Correct.
But why would you want to die?
[C.C.]
It's providence, a boundary.
Only when it's finite
can we call it life.
That's wrong! We call it
life because we feel it!
[C.C.] Same thing. There is
no life unless there is death.
That's just wordplay;
it's not real!
People die. That's real.
[LELOUCH]
Then why are we born at all?!
What's the purpose of it?
The meaning?!
You know the answer.
Those things are all
just illusions.
[LELOUCH] No! Living
just to die is too sad!
Without death, all we have are
random events... accumulation.
You can't call that life.
[LELOUCH gasps]
If you have a reason for living,
then you have to kill me.
Do that, and you'll
be Charles's equal.
You'll finally be
able to beat him.
So fare thee well, Lelouch.
You're too kind to
end our contract.
Wait! You're-- [screams]
[C.C.] Charles, why did
you steal V.V.'s Code?
Is there any point in
asking such questions?
After all, you're about to die.
I suppose you're right.
[LOHMEYER]
So very well then,
I'll proceed with
the redevelopment
of the Saitama ghetto
according to this schedule.
Wait a minute, please.
[LOHMEYER]
Huh?
[NUNNALLY]
Here.
[LOHMEYER]
Is something wrong?
[NUNNALLY]
This plan you worked out,
it isn't going to penalize
the Elevens, is it?
Of course not.
It's the best possible plan
for them and for us.
[NUNNALLY]
That is a lie, isn't it?
[gasps]
[NUNNALLY] Please rework
the plan once more.
I don't wish the Elevens
to be disadvantaged by it.
Princess, I am an expert.
Please let me handle the--
Miss Lohmeyer! I-I believe
that I... I'm the viceroy!
[SUZAKU]
After all this,
my only choice is to confront
Lelouch about it directly!
[RIVALZ]
Huh?
Suzaku did you finish
your work at the bureau?
[SUZAKU]
Have you seen Lelouch?
Uh-uh. I guess what happened
to Shirley really shook him up.
He hasn't been
home or at school.
[SUZAKU]
Hey!
[meow]
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
Where's Lelouch Lamperouge now?!
There is no unusual activity.
I asked where he is!
Where's Commander Villetta?!
Where's his "brother" Rolo?!
As I said, there's no
unusual activity to report.
[OSI AGENT B]
It's the same as always.
So that's it. The entire
O.S.I. staff has been...
Please forgive me. I had
to speak with Nunnally.
It's all right. We're
still getting ready.
[KANON]
What happened?
[SCHNEIZEL]
Oh, you know the topic.
Lloyd's Camelot
group and Suzaku.
[KANON]
I meant with the Toromo Agency.
Oh, that.
It depends on the
results of this test.
[NUNNALLY] Yes. My brother
Schneizel contacted me.
We can raise Area 11's
status to satellite region.
He said it's in
recognition of improved
public order
and productivity.
[SUZAKU]
That's good news.
[SUZAKU] Lelouch must
have been Zero all this time.
But if I report that
to the Emperor,
what happens to Nunnally?
[EMPEROR] If Lelouch
regains his memories,
then I shall simply use
Nunnally to deal with him.
Suzaku, you're not
hiding anything, right?
[SUZAKU]
Of course not.
You're the one person
that I'd never lie to.
[NUNNALLY]
Then will you tell me who it was
I spoke to on the
phone that time?
[SUZAKU gasps]
[NUNNALLY]
Wasn't it my big brother?
[SUZAKU gasping]
[NUNNALLY]
Suzaku...
You're just like him, aren't
you? Like my brother...
He's gone? Zero's gone?
[KINOSHITA] Yes. We received
a signal that he'd sighted
the target, but he and the
Shinkiro are missing.
[ROLO]
Missing? My brother is...?!
[LELOUCH]
Where am I?
Uh! Hey!
[LELOUCH gasping]
[C.C.]
It's no use.
These are all my memories.
You can't interfere.
[LELOUCH] C.C... No.
You're not, are you?
Who are you? Tell me.
I'm Lelouch. I am your...
[FEM NUN] Do you have some
reason to live, child?
[C.C.] I don't know.
I just don't want to die!
Then let's make a contract.
I will give you a special
power so you can survive.
And in return, one day you
will grant me a special wish.
Do you swear that you'll do it?
[LELOUCH]
So is this...?
[C.C.] It is. I swore to
uphold that contract.
Stop it! Stop it,
both of you! Please!
[SAYOKO]
I'm sorry about this.
We were getting along
quite well together.
[OHGI]
Stop! [groans]
[SAYOKO gasps]
[VILLETTA]
Ohgi!
[C.C.] The Geass I manifested
was to make people love me.
Love you?
[C.C.]
Because, deep in my heart, I...
I wanted to be
loved by someone.
[C.C.]
And my wish was granted.
Because of my Geass,
I was loved by everyone.
But in the end it was too much.
Love without limit was love
without meaning. I forgot
what love really was.
The only person I
believed in was her.
Because my Geass
couldn't work on her,
she was the one person who would
scold me for being trivial.
And yet...
[C.C.]
Yes yes...
I gave back all the gifts I
received, like you told me to.
But it can't be helped, can it?
It's because of the Geass.
I'm grateful to you Sister,
but this is a pain for me, too.
I'm so tired of all the
proposals and flowers.
Now some of them are starting
a religion around me!
[NUN]
Then shall we end it?
Huh?
[NUN] I need someone to take
my place. Someone with a Geass
that's exceptionally strong, so
eternity can finally end for me.
Can you imagine the agony?
The hell of living on
and on for eternity?
[C.C.]
Uh, what are you talking about?
I'm sorry, dear!
I'm afraid I tricked you!
[gasps]
[C.C.] She had just pretended
to be friends with me
right from the start.
I was a tool,
a way for her to end
her life. That's all.
[C.C.]
You're still not in here.
That means you're
not from my past.
You're a real person,
aren't you?
[LELOUCH]
Am I? I couldn't really say.
[C.C.] I wonder if you're
very important to me.
[LELOUCH]
That's impossible.
[C.C.] Oh? The fact you
were sent here means
I once tried to save you
from something. Or someone.
[LELOUCH]
Huh?
[C.C.] The people who hated me,
the ones who were kind to me.
All of them eventually vanished
into the flow of time,
the endless flow of eternity...
[EMPEROR]
But now, your tormented days...
[C.C.] Yes. They're over now.
My long journey ends here.
[LELOUCH]
C.C.!
[gasps]
[EMPEROR] You've opened it,
Lelouch! The Thought Elevator!
I see it now! This
realm of existence
is itself is a system for
interfering with thought!
[grunts]
[EMPEROR]
Soon it will be over.
Lelouch, sit where
you are and watch!
[LELOUCH gasps]
[C.C. gasping]
Stop it! C.C. is my...
She's my...!
Tell me, C.C...
Why didn't you make
me take your place?!
You could've had
your death that way!
Forcing me into your
hell of eternal life!
C.C., it wasn't out
of pity?! Was it?
[C.C. whimpers]
Don't die looking like that!
You should come
to death smiling!
I promise you the smile
you never had! Please...!
[C.C. grunts]
[EMPEROR] What do you think
you're doing, C.C.?!
You have stolen enough
from me already, Father!
You won't have her, too!
No! No, you'll ruin it all!
I know what it was now! I
understand what your Geass was!
And I know your true wish!
Come closer.
Let me reach you!
[DALLAS A] F.L.E.I.J.A.
Activation confirmed.
[KANON sighs]
It worked.
I can't believe
the explosive force!
Chief. Congratulations!
[NINA] Oh, no. The whole staff
at Invogue deserves the credit.
You'll have to accept
the compliment, Nina.
You are a genius.
I'm very honored,
Prince Schneizel.
Now war itself will change,
and mankind with it.
Damocles is here at last!
[LELOUCH]
Hey! We're back, C.C.! Wake up!
[gasps]
I've already contacted Rolo.
We'll use him to
get out of here.
Who are you, sir?
[LELOUCH]
What are you saying?
We need to talk about
the Emperor and that--
Are you my new master?
[LELOUCH]
Uh.
[C.C.] I-I can clean and help
prepare food for cooking.
I can also fetch water
and tend cows and sew.
I can read a little
and count to twenty.
Oh. I can carry away corpses,
if you need that.
[LELOUCH] Kallen has been
captured, Shirley is dead.
And now I've lost C.C. as well.
Even so, this is no time to
wallow in sentimentality!
I have a plan to
rescue Nunnally.
The problem is timing.
When to strike.
Even if we move now, there are
too many uncertain elements
waiting for the aftermath.
If I want to be sure of this,
I'll need a United
Federation of Nations.
And for that, keeping the
Emperor in that other realm
will be an absolute requirement.
But...