[C.C.]
Imperial calendar year 2017.
The colony of Japan,
now re-named Area 11,
declared a war of independence
against the suzerain state of
the Holy Britannian Empire.
This uprising, which came to be
known as the Black Rebellion,
was marked by heavy bloodshed
and ended with the second
historic defeat for Japan.
Since then, one
year has passed.
The terrorist known
as Zero, presumed dead,
has again appeared in Area 11.
Zero leads an armed
group of Japanese
known as the Black Knights.
His true identity:
Lelouch Lamperouge,
the exiled prince of
the Britannian Empire.
[ZERO] Therefore, once
again, here and now,
I declare the establishment of
the United States of Japan!
Starting from this moment,
this room shall be the
first dominion of the USJ!
Race, ideology, and
religion will not matter!
Being a citizen will have
but one requirement:
To do that which is just!
I came here to kill...
...Zero.
[phone rings]
It's my cell phone.
Nothing else.
[LELOUCH]
Rolo! Are you okay?!
[ROLO gasps]
Lelouch?!
Thank heaven!
I was getting really worried
because I couldn't
get a hold of you.
You aren't hurt, are you?
You're somewhere safe, right?
[ROLO]
What's going on here?
Is the Zero making the speech
right now a different person?
Uh, Big Brother,
where are you right now?
Me? What are you talkin' about?
Especially since-- Huh?
Hello, Rolo, it's me.
M-Miss Villetta?!
Lelouch came back to school,
and he's making up all the
classes that he missed.
You should get back
here soon, too.
Yes, ma'am, I understand.
Well, then? Are you finished
with your phone call?
It seems all my business...
is finished here.
The rag-tag remnants
of the Black Knights
and the man claiming to be
Zero are currently hiding in
a section of the Chinese
Federation consulate.
However, there is
no cause for alarm.
Acting Viceroy Guilford has
taken command of the army
in the absence of
wounded Viceroy Calares...
--[door opens]
--[footsteps]
You have the town
jumping, Lelouch.
[C.C.]
Naturally.
[KALLEN]
Uh?!
[C.C.] A new nation
has just been created
in their own territory.
And not to mention, of course,
that it also just
declared war on Britannia.
What's the matter?
When did you two switch places?
[C.C.]
Before the speech.
But I...
[C.C.]
His voice was re-recorded.
The moment "he" appeared,
it was already me.
Just like in a magic show.
You planned it on your own.
We don't like it when
you keep secrets from us.
[C.C.]
"We" don't like it?
You mean, you don't
like it. Do you?
[KALLEN grunts]
Lelouch, open the oven!
[LELOUCH]
Yeah, yeah.
Some salt.
Frying pan.
A fresh egg.
Bechemel sauce.
Put the gelato
on another plate.
Oh, and add the
rosemary to the sorbet.
Then, add the dill
to the sauerkraut.
The Black Forest Cake--
I can't do this by myself!
Why do you only keep asking
me to help with it all?
We didn't have a choice.
Rivalz has no sense of taste.
And of course, she is..
[SHIRLEY groans, screams]
Well, after all, she isn't
the most focused
person in the world.
[MILLY] Oh, just behave and
do what you're told, now.
Usually, a character like you,
would act as the type who
couldn't earn a living.
And he keeps a book of
his household spending.
[LELOUCH]
How'd you know that?!
[RIVALZ]
Oh, jeez, you really do?!
--[clanging]
--[SHIRLEY screams]
[RIVALZ]
Want a towel?
I will get it myself, thank you.
President, can I ask something?
Certainly, although I may
choose not to answer you.
So today... we are celebrating
Rolo and me coming back alive.
[MILLY]
Mm-hm!
You two escaped that
terror attack, all right!
Shirley was practically out
of her mind, the poor girl!
"Oh! If my Lulu's
been killed, I'll--"
[SHIRLEY screaming]
--[screaming continues]
--Hey, where is Rolo?
[MILLY] I spoke with
him, but, you know...
The boy's a lot more sensitive
than his older brother.
That's partly why he doesn't
have any friends, isn't it?
You should simply
say he's quiet!
[MILLY]
Uh...
Not that I mind your dirty hands
on my mouth, but...
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
--[RIVALZ laughing]
--[SHIRLEY] Look at this mess!
[LELOUCH] Nobody remembers
anything about Nunnally.
My little sister's been replaced
by a pretend little brother.
I wasn't the only one
whose memory was rewritten.
The entire student council has
been manipulated with, as well!
How dare they!
[AGENT A] Even after the
Babel Tower incident,
Lelouch Lamperouge has
shown no special changes.
[AGENT B]
There are 180 cameras on campus,
as well as 47
undercover observers.
That's 48 observers.
We've found no clues or
information that could
connect Lelouch with the
destruction of Carthage's unit.
Surveillance is perfect.
He has no opportunity
to use his Geass.
If he is Zero, it would be odd
if he returned
here to the school.
[ROLO]
And what's the status of C.C.?
Where is she?
If she's not in close
proximity to Lelouch, then...
...the odds are very slim that
she would be in the consulate.
[ROLO]
You mean things are the same
as they were before
the incident?
You've still no clue
where C.C. is?
[VILLETTA grunts]
Those of us in the Office
of Secret Intelligence
will carry on our
mission to capture her!
People, continue observing
the bait as you have been.
[AGENTS]
Yes, My Lord.
[LELOUCH]
The enemy's center is
where their surveillance
data is transmitted.
I can just keep acting
the way I have been,
but the problem is Nunnally.
The fact that all memory of her
has been erased from
everyone's minds
tells me she would never
show up here at school.
In short, the
probability is high
that the Britannian
emperor has my sister now.
I'm dealing with a man who would
use his own children as pawns.
If they learn that I've
regained my memories...
that I've reverted
to being Zero...
Nunnally will be in danger!
I have to plan my
movements carefully.
First, I'll trick the people
they have spying on me.
And then...
[VILLETTA]
Lelouch?
[LELOUCH gasps]
[VILLETTA] Make sure you come
to class tomorrow, you hear?
Yes, I hear you.
Coach Villetta, you really
should have more faith in me.
[LELOUCH]
Villetta Nu...
A woman I once used my Geass on.
[LELOUCH] I can use my Geass
power on a person only once.
Which means... it won't
work on her any more.
That leaves my brother Rolo,
who shouldn't even exist.
Why don't I begin by
gradually subduing him?
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[FRENCH GENERAL]
Italian state forces are
holding strong on
the right flank, too!
[FRENCH OFFICER]
The victory Bordeaux
we drink tonight will
be a fine vintage!
Unknown craft
approaching from above!
What?!
[EU 1]
The Lancelot!
[EU 2]
Britannia's White Death!
[EU 1] Knights of the Round
here at the front line?!
[SUZAKU]
Please surrender.
--[EU SOLDIERS] Huh? What?
--[SUZAKU] You have no
chance of winning.
Anyone who throws his weapon
down will not be shot.
Of all the impertinent--!
Destroy him, dammit!
He's only one knight!
Then so be it.
[SUZAKU]
Do you want more?!
[KANON] Allowing him to
conduct a solo operation?
Are you sure?
Kururugi used to be your
subordinate, Your Highness.
[SCHNEIZEL]
He's now the Knight of Seven
and reports directly
to His Majesty.
Yes, My Lord...
He has been elevated in rank.
He's to be admired.
The world today is
overflowing with despair.
That's why he uses his humility
and sense of duty as a compass
to guide him through
these dark times.
[LELOUCH]
Nina's gone, too.
I wonder if Suzaku
took Arthur with him.
Huh?
[ROLO]
What's up?
How come you're looking
through the album?
Hey, that's the student council
marathon dance file, isn't it?
You know the Prez.
She runs us ragged with
all these events
she likes to put on.
[ROLO] Oh, that's the
Broken Heart Contest.
[LELOUCH chuckles]
Talk about sad irony.
The Prez stomps
on Rivalz's heart
then presents him with
the award for winning.
[laughs]
Weird how you
happened to escape.
[LELOUCH]
Hm?
[ROLO]
You heard the news, didn't you?
Our military had Babel Tower
completely surrounded.
So how did you do it? How did
you manage to get past them?
What're you talking about, Rolo?
Do you wanna know how I
got away from the military,
or did you mean
to say terrorists?
[ROLO gasps]
I took an emergency corridor.
I tried to call you,
but my cell wouldn't work
in that particular area.
I see.
[LELOUCH]
A locket...
That's right.
I remember giving it to
Rolo for his birthday.
No, that's wrong.
October 25th... is
not his birthday.
It's Nunnally's birthday!
Rolo, give me that locket.
[ROLO]
Huh?
I don't know what
I was thinking.
That's not a good
gift for a guy.
I'll get you something else--
Don't take it! You gave
it to me! It's mine!
Please don't!
Don't take it back!
Uh... Sure, fine.
You keep it then, Rolo.
[ROLO]
Uh...
Right.
We haven't observed any changes
in Lelouch's behavior.
There are no indications that
he's used his Geass, either.
[VILLETTA] The order won't
divulge the secrets of Geass
due to its religious nature--
[ROLO gasps]
[AGENT K] Uh, sorry, I can
see you're busy. It can wait.
[ROLO grunts]
[VILLETTA gasps]
Rolo, no! He's one of us!
He's on the same
mission we are--
Wait for orders! [gasps]
[ROLO] There's a chance
he overheard us.
Knowledge of Geass is restricted
to just us two in
the Tokyo section!
We can't take the risk!
But still...
How many of our agents
have you killed so far?
It was the quickest and
most certain method
to keeping the secret.
Or am I wrong?
[KALLEN]
It's been three days
since the United States
of Japan was established.
I doubt Britannia is going to
keep glaring at us indefinitely.
There's even talk about
ousting the consul-general
back in the Chinese
Federation's homeland.
And yet, we still
haven't received
any instructions from Lelouch.
What on earth is he doing?
[KALLEN]
You really are Zero, aren't you?
[gasps]
Of course!
[GAO-HAI]
I can drag out
the extradition negotiations
with the Britannians.
I think I might be able
to buy us up to a week.
I'll report that to Zero.
As for the Chinese
Federation government's--
[KALLEN]
C.C.! I was just thinking!
Wouldn't it have made more sense
for you to have
played the bunny girl?!
[gasps]
Huh?!
Uh!
[gasps, screams]
Zero is... a girl?!
Correct.
I'm not Zero!
[C.C.]
Oh, you let on too soon.
You have no sense
of humor, do you?
Don't play around with Zero!
[C.C.]
We
[KALLEN gasps, screams]
It's a pleasure to meet
you, Ms. Kallen Kouzuki.
You're the pilot of the
Guren MK-II, right?
[KALLEN gasps]
How did you--
I'm someone who takes an
avid interest in you people.
--[door opens]
--[XING-KE gasps]
[BLACK KNIGHT]
There's trouble!
It's Ohgi and the
other prisoners!
[KALLEN gasps]
[GUILFORD]
Can you hear me, Zero?
Listen closely. I am Lord
Gilbert G.P. Guilford,
knight of her royal highness,
Cornelia li Britannia!
Beginning tomorrow
at 15:00 hours,
these 256 special
class A felons,
--who are guilty of treason
--They wouldn't...
[GUILFORD]
against the empire,
will all be executed
for their crimes!
[GUILFORD]
Zero!
If you value the lives of your
people, then you will face me,
one-on-one, in an
honorable duel!
[LELOUCH] Guilford... You've
really gone and done it now.
Lulu! Are you in here
all by yourself?
Yeah. Shirley, don't you
have swim club now?
Yes, I do, but...
You see, I have to go shopping
because I have to
buy a birthday gift.
[LELOUCH]
Whose birthday?
Ms. Villetta, our counselor.
They all agree I should buy it,
since I'm always the one
who always gets her mad.
Problem is,
I'm incredibly impaired
at picking out presents.
She seems to enjoy liquor,
I could buy her that.
But I don't know what
brand she likes.
Should I go with you?
Huh?!
I could help you select
a present for her.
[SHIRLEY gasps]
[SHIRLEY]
Y-You would?! Seriously?!
[LELOUCH]
Sure. You ready to go?
[SHIRLEY]
Yeah! Mm-hm!
All right! Now I've got
my scoop! Thank you, guys!
[C.C.] Since you're unable
to control your Geass,
this is for your protection.
[LELOUCH] It only has
to block optical data,
so a normal color contact
lens would work fine,
Don't try to probe
for information.
As you've already guessed,
you're holding a special lens.
Although...
Should your Geass grow stronger
than what you have now--
Well, we'll just have
to end this game...
...before that happens.
[LELOUCH gasps]
Are you're going out?
Yeah, I have to help
pick out a gift.
It's a present for
Ms. Villetta's birthday.
Her birthday?
I see.
I guess birthdays are
important, aren't they?
Well, I'd better be going.
[ROLO]
See you later.
[MILLY]
Rolo!
[ROLO]
Huh? Ah!
[MILLY chuckling]
Miss President!
--Rolo, you come along, too!
--[ROLO] Huh?
It'll be fun to chat.
[LELOUCH]
Hm...
I've learned about wines
but never tried any.
[SHIRLEY]
Outta luck there.
How about this stuff?
[LELOUCH]
Maybe those are too sweet.
How 'bout a Sopron?
[SHIRLEY]
Could this be...
...a date?
If it's not...
...I'll make it one, then!
[LELOUCH]
Just as I planned.
Although, I didn't think
they'd bring Rolo, too.
Typical of Milly...
What a great topic
for our next meeting
of the Society of Research
on Male-Female Dating!
Um... Right.
Yeah, but it fair for him
to follow his own brother?
You're as interested
as we are, aren't you?
She may end up being
your family member.
[RIVALZ]
She's right!
Family...
[AGENT] Target is taking
assumed route "Zebra."
[VILLETTA]
Roger. Switch off with Group 7.
Group 2, watch for
contact with C.C.
[AGENT] Yes, My Lord.
Cleaning the perimeter.
[ROLO] Can it be that
he really isn't Zero?
[LELOUCH] They specifically
set a trap at Babel Tower.
Which means my enemy isn't
the settlement's
vice-regal government.
While I can't tell for
certain who's watching me,
the system itself that
they're using has flaws in it.
[VILLETTA]
If he is Zero,
he won't ignore the execution
of his people tomorrow.
Maybe his memory truly
hasn't returned.
[LELOUCH]
Excuse me.
How do I fill this part out?
[CLERK]
Pardon?
Sorry, but could you
do me a favor, please?
Sure. What can I do for you?
[LELOUCH]
Well, it's like this...
[SHIRLEY]
Mmm...
Huh?
[SHIRLEY gasps]
--[LELOUCH] I'm back.
--[SHIRLEY yelps]
What were you looking at?
Oh! Um... That!
[SHIRLEY]
I... was just wishing
I could take a ride on
a cable car sometime.
--[laughs]
--[LELOUCH gasps]
[LELOUCH]
It's my fault.
My fault that Shirley's
memories were wiped.
Milly and Rivalz, too!
Their memories re-written
without their consent!
I just can't let things
go the way they are.
When this is all over...
I swear I'll--
[SHIRLEY]
What's the matter?
[LELOUCH] The Prez and the
others are following us.
What? Where?
[LELOUCH]
Shirley.
[SHIRLEY]
Huh?
I thought of a terrific idea.
[AGENT A]
Target entering store.
Alpha-14. It's a small shop.
There's a risk I'll blow
my cover if I follow.
Cover the front of the place.
I'll send three people
to cover the rear.
Okay.
All I want you do to is pretend
that I'm in here for a while.
What are you gonna do?
[LELOUCH] I'm going to
sneak out of the store
and surprise the
Prez and the others.
Sure! I gotcha!
[LELOUCH]
I don't normally shop here.
I hope they don't have any
surveillance cameras
or microphones.
Shirley thinks this is
only a harmless prank.
Even on the off-chance
that something goes wrong,
I won't cause any
trouble for her.
I used my Geass to
make the preparations.
Now all I have to do...
[phone rings]
Hello, Omotessando Mall
security; may I help you?
Huh?! The Black Knights?!
We have planted a bomb in the
mall, and we will detonate it
if all our following demands
are not met immediately.
[ROLO]
No... He can't be Zero!
[chiming tone]
[PA] Paging Mr. Maximillian
from the Hakodate settlement.
Paging Mr. Maximillian from
the Hakodate settlement.
--You have a phone call.
--That means a...!
A terrorist warning!
It must be the Black Knights!
Zero's been resurrected!
Keep your voices down!
The customers will hear!
[CLERK 1]
But...!
[ROLO]
Uh?
A bomb threat has just been made
to Omotessando Mall, My Lord!
Okay, hold your positions!
Prepare for contact from C.C.!
[LELOUCH] All tasks at
hand have been cleared,
except for the detonator.
10... 9... 8... 7...
...6... 5... 4... 3...
...2... 1...!
[alarm rings]
It's the Black Knights!
[screams]
Terrorists?!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[AGENT X groans]
What's happening?!
What the hell?!
Whoa, what's going on?!
--Rolo!
--Rolo! Don't run off!
Rolo?
[ROLO gasps]
He's gone!
We've lost the target, M'Lord!
What should we do about the info
that we've got from Scorpion?
Where's Rolo?!
All cell phone calls are being
jammed to maintain civic order!
My Lord, should we act on
Scorpion's info or not?!
Very well, I'll go myself!
[PEOPLE screaming]
--[screaming continues]
--[LELOUCH laughs]
[LELOUCH]
And that's just one easy way...
...to cause a panic.
What's his location?!
Uh?!
No one's here. Where are they?
[ROLO gasps]
[LELOUCH] It seems they've
gone looking for C.C...
I see.
You really have awakened.
[LELOUCH] I put the man
who was following me
under my absolute control
and turned him into my slave.
Just as I thought, your top
priority was the capture of C.C.
No matter how wrong the
information is that you get.
--[laughs]
--[ROLO grunts]
As of this moment, this
gilded prison of a school
will become my castle,
my fortress of freedom.
And as for you, dear brother,
I'll make you my pawn
to find Nunnally.
[gasps] What?!
[LELOUCH]
Geass?!
You stopped time?!
[ROLO]
Lelouch...
Now you and your demonic eye...
...will die.
[explosion]
[KALLEN gasps]
[BLACK KNIGHT]
Zero! Emergency!
--The Chinese Federation just--
--[XING-KE yells]
Huh?!
[BLACK KNIGHT groans]
[BLACK KNIGHT whimpers]
Here and now, you cursed Black
Knights will be vanquished!
[LELOUCH]
Guilford is about to exectue
the core members of
the Black Knights.
The very people I need in
order to carry out my plan!
Somehow, I have to save them.
But at the moment,
my phony brother Rolo
is my main obstacle.
It's only logical that
they would assign a
Geass-user to observe me.
But that power of his...
No...
There's a breach I can exploit.
For the sake of everyone whose
memories were rewritten, I must!