This is the first
time in eight years
I've seen your face.
The face of a brother
and a murderer.
[grunts]
[NUNNALLY] And I wear
the same face, as well,
don't I, Lelouch?
[LELOUCH]
Then...
It's been you firing the
F.L.E.I.J.A.s up until now.
[NUNNALLY] Yes. I wanted to
stop it all. To stop you.
I would have done
whatever I had to,
even if it meant
killing my big brother.
That's why I can't allow
you to have control
of the F.L.E.I.J.A.s...
Why I can't hand
this key to you.
And I wouldn't even if you--
Even if you used
your Geass on me!
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Use Geass on Nunnally?
It's true.
Time after time, I've
wanted to use it on her.
At the very least, I wanted to
use it to cure her blindness.
The power of the king...
But Nunnally was the reason
for everything I've done,
so I could never
use Geass' power
of absolute submission on her.
But now... No, I can't!
If I resort to twisting
my own sister's will...
...then I'm...!
[growls]
[SUZAKU] Kallen... Are you
determined to defy me?
[KALLEN] It's clear to me now
that I misjudged you, Suzaku.
[SUZAKU]
Hm?
Even though we're
on opposite sides
and our methods differ
from one another,
I always thought you cared
about Japan in your way.
But now...!
[SUZAKU]
There's something that I...
...that Lelouch
and I have to do.
[KALLEN]
I see...
You really crave
power that much?
In that case...
[SUZAKU]
In that case, what?
You mustn't be allowed
to live, Suzaku.
I'm going to defeat
you and stop Lelouch!
[SUZAKU]
No, that won't happen!
You having any second thoughts
about not running away?
Just where exactly
would I be running to?
[chuckles] You have
a point, Rivalz.
What I wish for...
...is to enjoy fun-filled days
with the old gang again,
the way we used to.
Mm. I do miss them.
You, power without a master!
You, who has to have
something to depend on.
A weak man!
Stop, please! You're
too badly wounded!
No, I have to
take responsibility
for starting this!
Because that's what
allows me the right
to lead others!
[NUNNALLY] Lelouch, you
have no right to seize
control of the world.
You, of all people,
who took the name Zero then
bent the will of so many
in order to serve your own!
[LELOUCH] Are you saying we
would have been better off
to remain in hiding? Did you
want a future of living
in constant fear
of assassination?
This was for your
future, too, Nunnally.
My future?!
When did I ever say
that I wanted this?!
Lelouch...
I would have been
perfectly satisfied
by just living with you!
Don't you see?
Our reality is restricted
by all sorts of things!
Our whole history is struggle!
[KALLEN] That's the reason
I've been fighting
on the side of the resistance!
[SUZAKU]
You could have used the system
to achieve your ideals!
But what about the others?!
Those people who aren't
allowed into the system?
How will they ever
be able to voice
their objections to anything?!
[SUZAKU]
You...!
[KALLEN] Don't you dare look
down on others, you elitist!
[SUZAKU] What about
those who've no choice
but to join the system?!
What's fair?!
[TOHDOH] When you follow the
methods of an aggressor,
then you're only serving
to legitimize them.
[CHIBA] But, if you go into
battle now, you'll die!
Why you...! And you
call yourself a--!
[gasps]
I apologize.
Huh?
[TOHDOH grunts, gasps]
This is the only way
I know how to live.
[CHIBA]
Kyoshiro!
Why do people always
have to fight?!
I fight because
there is something
that I must protect!
[CORNELIA] It may be that
we can no longer find
morality or a sense of
dignity in our warfare.
[VILLETTA] Regardless, I still
needed to belong somewhere.
[OHGI] For that reason
alone, we fought.
Naoto... This is really
the best thing for us?
[LLOYD]
You know what they say,
war is the mother of invention.
[RAKSHATA]
Nonsense, Earl of Pudding.
You don't care one
bit whether or not
your invention benefits mankind.
Nina, was it?
What about you, huh?
I was just... doing
whatever I could.
You see, we simply didn't
want it to happen again.
Oh?
However, people are
subject to weakness.
[TAMAKI] That's right!
Even I have dreams, don't I?!
But now they're
telling me I don't have
any right to them!
They don't think I'm
able to fight, but I can!
Why does everyone
treat me like a fool?!
Poor guy.
[C.C.]
I've seen it before.
I've seen it over and over.
Human history is one
of struggle. Even so...
The world and the
people in it...
They'll never be what
we want them to be!
[KALLEN]
So now you'll force them?!
That's your solution?!
That's plain--
[NUNNALLY]
Despicable!
Using Geass, a power that
manipulates the minds
of people and violates
their human dignity.
[LELOUCH]
Then what about the Damocles?
So would you agree that's
a despicable method
that forces people to obey?!
The Damocles...
...will become the
symbol of their hatred.
[LELOUCH gasps]
All their hatred
will be focused here.
That way, people can
move toward the future.
[LELOUCH] I see. You have
the same idea, Nunnally.
In that case...
Lelouch vi Britannia
commands you!
Hand over the Damocles
key to me now!
[gasps]
No!
No, I mustn't give it
to you! I mustn't do it!
All the sins...
...you've... committed!
Take this. It's yours now.
[JEREMIAH grunts]
Why you impudent--!
Memorized recording complete.
[JEREMIAH]
Not quite!
[gasps]
Fire!
Memorize this! Memorize
Jeremiah Gottwald!
Commit it to memory,
because that's
the memorable name of the
man who has defeated you!
Memory? What memory?
I remember nothing,
I have no memories.
[JEREMIAH]
No memories? Could it be...?
C'mon, Tristan, move it!
Just let me fly, will ya?
The radiant wave
surger's out of ammo.
Now my shield energy
is exhausted, too?
[KALLEN]
Big deal!
[SUZAKU]
I can't beat her!
Even using the Geass
I'm cursed with!
Your strength is
unimaginable, Kallen!
My machine has better
specs than yours, yet...
Why...? While you're
this strong...
Do the right thing!
Let's end this once and for all!
If only you had
justice on your side!
What happened?
You mean I didn't get him, then?
You're wrong. You got me,
all right... Kallen.
You won. You beat him, Kallen.
Nunnally...
...you've grown up
following your own thoughts,
without help from others.
Which means, I am now
free to follow the path
I must take to my destiny.
I thank you.
I love you, little sister.
[NUNNALLY]
Huh?
You used your Geass
on me, didn't you?!
Come back!
[NUNNALLY gasps]
Stop, Lelouch! Wait--
You've become a demon, Lelouch!
Despicable!
Cowardly!
How can you? How can
you be so cruel?
[NUNNALLY sobs]
[KAGUYA] The traitorous
knight, Suzaku Kururugi,
has reportedly been killed.
Aren't you going to beg
for your life to be spared?
Even for his sake, at least?
[C.C.]
Kaguya...
You never knew Lelouch's
true face until recently,
isn't that right?
[KAGUYA]
What of it?
Well, in spite of that,
you still understood
a bit of his true nature.
So you're obviously
a very kind young woman.
Huh?
[rumbling]
[KAGUYA, BLACK KNIGHTS gasp]
[LELOUCH]
Attention, entire world!
Hear my proclamation!
I am Lelouch vi Britannia,
emperor of the Holy Britannian
Empire and your only ruler!
It's not possible!
If Lelouch used a F.L.E.I.J.A.,
then that means...!
It can't be!
There's no way!
[LELOUCH]
Schneizel has surrendered to me!
As a result of this, I am
now in control of both
the Damocles and the
F.L.E.I.J.A. weapons!
And even the
Black Knights no longer
possess the strength
to oppose me now!
If anyone dares to resist
my supreme authority,
they shall know the devastating
power of the F.L.E.I.A.s!
Those who could challenge
my military rule
no longer exist!
Yes!
From this day, from
this moment forward,
the world belongs to me!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[LELOUCH] Lelouch vi
Britannia commands you!
Obey me, subjects!
Obey me, world!
All hail Lelouch!
[SOLDIERS IN KNIGHTMARES]
[ANNOUNCER]
And now, just coming into view,
is the 99th and sole emperor
of the Holy Britannian Empire,
His Majesty
Lelouch vi Britannia.
Our emperor also
carries the distinction
of being CEO of the
Black Knights, as well as
the current chairman of
the U.F.N. Supreme Council.
And look at this, too.
Those who foolishly
opposed Emperor Lelouch
are being transported
to the execution grounds.
During the latest
great war, the capital,
Pendragon, was destroyed
and countless soldiers
sacrificed their
lives, among them,
Sir Suzaku Kururugi,
the Knight of Zero.
Now that the E.U.
has ratified the United
Federation of Nations charter,
the emperor has allowed us
to complete the grand task
of unifying the world!
Glory to His Majesty Lelouch!
All hail Britannia!
All Hail Lelouch!
[MAN 1 IN CROWD]
Glory, my ass.
[MAN 2 IN CROWD]
This is just a dictatorship.
[MAN 3 IN CROWD] Anyone who
disobeys him gets killed!
[WOMAN IN CROWD]
Shh!
If the wrong people hear you,
they'll kill your entire family!
[BROADCASTER] I can't believe
we have to broadcast this
and call it justice!
[RIVALZ] Lelouch...
is this what you wanted?
What you set out to do?
To control the world? To
control every person in it?!
[RAKSHATA]
None of you were very bright.
If you hadn't disobeyed
Lelouch at that time...
[NINA]
We had to move into the future.
[RAKSHATA]
Hm?
[CECILE] It's through repeated
successes and failures
that we advance.
That not only goes for
science, but people, as well.
But that's evolution.
You mean progress,
don't you, Earl of Pudding?
About that name you call me...
[RAKSHATA]
Hm?
Are you still bitter?
I could be. I could be not.
What's up with them,
Professor Lloyd
and Miss Rakshata?
[CECILE]
Hm?
[NINA] Did something once
happen between them?
It's hardly worth mentioning.
And when I think back on it now,
it wasn't anything at all.
It was just a starting point.
[VILLETTA gasps]
Ohgi!
Do that, and you'll play
right into their hands!
But he's...!
[CROWD gasping murmuring]
[SOLIDER IN KNIGHTMARE]
What is that?
Zero?!
Huh? Zero?
[gasps] Zero?!
That's him?! But
Lelouch is over there!
Was that it?!
Was that what Lelouch
and Suzaku had to do?!
Cease fire!
I'll take care
of this interloper!
Hm?!
[JEREMIAH]
Onward, masked knight.
[gasps]
Impudent fool!
Heh.
[LELOUCH]
Suzaku... You have to kill me.
You must promise.
[SUZAKU]
You're going through with this?
No matter what?
[LELOUCH]
As planned...
The hatred of the whole world
is now focused directly upon me.
And now, the only
thing that remains
is to get rid of me and finally
break the cycle of hatred.
The legend of Zero isn't dead.
It lives within the hearts
of the Black Knights.
Schneizel will serve Zero, also.
With this, the
world will gather,
not for an exchange of
force, but for an exchange
of open dialog around one table.
Mankind will be able to
move forward into the future.
And that...
Yes.
[SUZAKU]
...is the Zero... Requiem.
[SUZAKU] We both realized
it back in Cs' world.
We knew how humanity was
longing for the future.
[LELOUCH laughs]
Hey, Suzaku, Geass power
is similar to a wish,
don't you think?
Huh?
It's a request to
someone to give you
the power to achieve what
you can't on your own.
A wish? No.
Yes. And I'm going to grant
a wish called Geass
to all the people everywhere.
For the future
of the entire world.
[C.C.]
Lelouch...
The price you're going to
pay for using your Geass
on them is a dear one.
The only ones who should kill
are those prepared to be killed.
[LELOUCH] Suzaku... You're
going to be a hero, now.
The messiah who saved the world
from Emperor
Lelouch vi Britannia,
the enemy of the world.
As Zero.
[gasps]
[SUZAKU]
L... Lelouch...!
The punishment for
what you've done
shall be this, then...
You will live on...
always wearing that mask,
serving as a knight
for justice and truth.
ou will no longer
live your life
as Suzaku Kururugi.
You shall sacrifice
the ordinary pleasures
of your life for the
benefit of the world...
For eternity...
[SUZAKU] This Geass...
I do solemnly accept.
Lelouch? Are you...?
[gasps]
You mean...
...everything you've
done until now...
Oh, big brother, I love you!
[LELOUCH]
Yes... I...
I destroy... the world...
...and create it...
[LELOUCH]
...anew...
[gasps]
You can't leave me!
You can't!
Please open your eyes,
big brother! Please...!
Big brother...!
Lelouch the demon is dead!
Free his prisoners!
[CROWD cheers]
This isn't good!
Everyone, retreat!
Is that... who I think it is?
It's Zero!
[TOHDOH]
Uh?!
It's him!
It's Zero!
It's unfair!
All I wanted and needed to
be happy was to be with you!
How can I ever look
forward the future
without you?
[CROWD chanting]
Zero! Zero! Zero!
[KALLEN]
Well, Lelouch...
The world's gotten a lot better
since that eventful day.
All the energy that
was once expended
on war has now
been directed toward
solving hunger and poverty.
As expected,
all sorts of hateful
and evil deeds have been
blamed on you. Hm...
Maybe that's because
people find it a lot easier
to accuse a person
with a name,
rather than a piece of
technology called Damocles.
Perhaps that's putting
it too simply.
But... whatever the reason...
...the world is free of
the past and it's finally
able to move forward
into the future now.
I wonder if you're
laughing right now
about how everything went
according to your
elaborate strategy.
Nevertheless, there are
still plenty of problems
we have to work
out for ourselves.
But even so...
I said that Geass was
the power of the king
which would condemn you
to a life of solitude.
I think maybe that's
not quite correct.
Right... Lelouch?