[C.C.] The actions
one takes are answered
by consequences waiting
at their conclusion.
There are no exceptions,
and even Lelouch's power
cannot change this.
Despite his absolute
ability to make anyone
obey him, there is no
escaping the inevitable.
Lelouch has acted to avenge
his mother's death,
and to create a world
where his younger sister,
Nunnally, can find happiness.
Now, he is confronted by
the results of his acts;
consequences he never imagined.
And there are more to come.
If these unintended
consequences help
to create new worlds,
who will bear the blame
for the sins that are committed?
Who will take the punishment?
And who will measure it out?
[PRIEST]
He was a pious soul,
who always looked
to God in his life.
And a friend to us all.
To his wife, he was
a devoted husband.
To his child, a loving father.
[SHIRLEY]
Father...
May he rest in peace,
forever cradled
in the bosom of our lord.
[SHIRLEY'S MOM]
No! Stop!
[MOURNERS gasp]
[SHIRLEY'S MOM]
Don't bury him again, please!
He's suffered enough!
Oh god, don't leave me...
Mom, he's gone already.
Please, Mom.
Guess what, Papa!
Some day, when I grow up,
I'm gonna be your wife!
[SHIRLEY'S DAD] Oh, that's
very sweet of you, honey.
But your teacher
told you, didn't she?
Huh?
[SHIRLEY'S DAD]
Someday, you'll meet the man
you really love.
More than I do you?
[SHIRLEY'S DAD]
Hm... It's hard to explain.
Well, if you truly
love that person,
and he cares for
you just as much...
It would make me the
happiest father on earth.
Shirley... I'm so
sorry this happened...
[SHIRLEY] Oh, stop. What've
you to apologize for?
[gasps]
[RIVALZ]
We feel awful!
Huh?
It's just that...
When we were all watching
the hotel jacking on TV...
I thought the Black Knights
were, ya know, heroes.
I mean, the news was
handling it all wrong!
Anyway, I was posting online
how I thought what
happened in Narita
was kinda cool and
I'm-- Forgive me!
Come on, don't be silly.
That has absoloutely nothing
to do with this at all.
I mean even I was
saying Narita wa--
Shirley, stop.
Seriously, I'm starting
to worry about you here.
Have you cried yet?
If you simply hold it in,
it's only gonna be
harder for you later on.
You don't have to worry.
Really, I'm fine.
I've cried a lot...
--[SUZAKU] Cowards!
--Huh?
Zero and his people,
their methods are just cowardly!
He doesn't even get
his hands dirty.
He stirs people into a frenzy,
tips the world into chaos,
and then sits back and
congratulates himself!
It's not going to
change a thing!
Anything gained through
his kind of tactics
is just meaningless!
Huh?
Well, anyway, I think it's time
we headed back, everyone.
Shirley, we'll be
waiting for you.
Back in the old
student council room.
Same as ever.
C'mon, guys, let's go.
Hey, uh, Lelouch...
What? Wha'd I do?
Lulu... Forgive me.
What?
It wasn't fair,
kissing you like that.
It wasn't fair of me at all.
It was just...
something I did...
Forget about it, okay?
I shouldn't have put you
on the spot like that.
I'm sorry. It was
totally stupid of me.
I mean, you finally kissed me,
and I can't even be happy!
Wait, I--! Shirley!
[phone vibrating]
[C.C.]
Do you regret it?
That your friend's father
was caught up in all this?
[gasps]
[C.C.]
You were just accusing Kirihara
of being too soft.
What happened to
the path of blood?
[LELOUCH]
Shut up.
[C.C.] But it turns out
you're the soft one.
Did you think was
all just a game?
You've already killed
your fair share of people.
By hand. Or words,
more often than not.
Just shut up.
All of them left
behind a family.
All had lovers and friends.
Are you really telling me
you hadn't grasped that yet?
I would've thought you
to be better prepared.
Just shut up! I am prepared!
I have been from the
moment I killed Clovis!
[C.C.]
Then why this hesitation?
Has she shaken you so badly?
One kiss and you go
to pieces then, huh?
[grunts]
Hm. So, for all your
preening and posturing,
you're really just
a spoiled little boy
with a swollen head
and a big fat mouth.
You're in way too deep
to be turning back now.
You've past the
point of no return.
You need a reason
for living, don't you?
You're not going to
disappoint me, are you?
[gasps]
[sputtering]
Yes!
That is why people discriminate
against one another.
So is that the reason why
you killed my brother?!
[SUZAKU] And any ends gained
through contemptible means
aren't worth anything.
[OHGI] Are you really
going through with this?
[KALLEN] That's easy
enough to say, isn't it?!
[CLOVIS] You can't! We may
have different mothers,
but you and I are still blood!
It's nothing but
self-satisfying gratification!
[C.C.]
And to have this utopia you'd...
[LELOUCH grunts]
I wish the world
was a gentler place.
[C.C.] You appear to
have a reason for living
And I've come back
to change everything.
Are you embarking
on the path of blood?
[LELOUCH grunts]
[LELOUCH]
Ohgi... It's me. Zero.
[car door clicks]
[footsteps, clothes rustle]
[TECH A]
Data logger S-4, contact.
[TECH B]
Protocol established.
[LLOYD]
I have some bad news, Suzaku!
We just got word from
Cornelia's Royal Guard!
We're on deck for
the next operation!
Huh?
[LLOYD] Are they
acknowledging your skill,
or do they need another decoy?
[CECILE]
Oh, Lloyd?
Huh?
Care for a lesson in
proper social etiquette?
You look like you have
some time to kill.
I'll have to take
a pass on that.
Now then, I believe we were
talking about your mission...
[OHGI sighs]
W-Wait a second, Zero!
I realize this is a
request from Kyoto.
I think we could
definitely handle it.
And, I'm pretty sure the
Japan Liberation Front
would rather join
with us than flee
to foreign soil and all, but--
[ZERO]
You're the one who brought us
this information...
Diethard, wasn't it?
That's right.
It is an honor that you'd
meet me like this, Zero.
[ZERO] So, Princess
Cornelia is going to deploy
the royal marines on Gen. Katase
of the Japan Liberation
Front. Is that correct?
[DIETHARD] Yes, the Network
is already poised
to broadcast a
special report on it.
[ZERO] Lt. Col. Toudou
will never make it
to Katase in time. Which means
the Japan Liberation
Front has no
military strength right now.
Their only chance of escape
is the liquid Sakuradite
they're carrying.
Which is why we should
help General Katase
escape instead of
going after Cornelia!
[ZERO]
Ohgi! Who are we?
W-We're the Black
Knights, Zero...
[ZERO]
Then we have but one task!
We will destroy Cornelia's
troops, and in doing so,
rescue the remnants of the JLF.
Tonight, we regain what
was lost to us at Narita!
[OHGI]
What're our chances?
[ZERO]
Need you ask?
Understood.
[DIETHARD]
Hm.
[ZERO]
Begin preparations.
You all have your
orders to carry out.
[KALLEN]
Uh--! Zero!
[ZERO]
I have something to attend to.
Whatever it is,
save it for later.
[DALTON]
Just so you know...
The viceroy has her reservations
about using Numbers.
But use every able
body, I always say.
Even if it's the son of
the former prime minister.
[SUZAKU grunts]
Our target is Katase.
Take him out and
the Japan Liberation
Front is finished.
We're sending in
the Royal Marines.
Your job'll be to
provide supporting fire
from the shore until the
marines have Katase...
...as well as annihilating
any stragglers left over.
[gasps] I'm to
annihilate them, sir?
Nobody but the
target is to survive,
is that clear?
[gasps]
[DALTON]
Warrant Officer Kururugi,
show your loyalty to the crown.
This your chance to get
ahead in the world, soldier.
Understood... my lord.
Onward, Christian soldiers.
Conflicting morals, right?
[SUZAKU grunts]
[SHIRLEY]
No, Lulu...
It can't be true...
He would never get tangled up
with someone like that...
[VILETTA] There is a
possibility that this boy
is linked to
the Black Knights.
What're you saying--
he's involved?
In terrorism.
I don't belive you!
He can't be...
It has to be a lie.
[SHIRLEY]
Lulu...
I'm so sorry to be doubting
you like this... But...
[SHIRLEY]
Please, I wanna believe in you!
[VILETTA]
Dammit, she lost him.
If she had just called me
sooner, I could've had him!
I should've grabbed him
when I had the chance.
No, I need proof.
If he talks to her, I can learn
what his role is in all this.
Which is all the more important
if he can manipulate
memory somehow.
[VILETTA]
I won't have to die,
stripped of my position
and honor, like Jeremiah.
Hell, this is my chance
to move back up again.
So, I have to find
a link to Zero...
It has to be me!
[door clangs]
[LELOUCH gasps]
Who's there?!
Ah! I-I'm sorry! I'll go...
[LELOUCH]
Second thoughts?
[gasps]
I thought the goal was justice.
The only reason I've
fought until now
is because I thought it
was the right thing to do.
So I could live with
the killing. But now...
Tell me is this real?!
Is what we're all
doing here really
going to change the
world for the better?!
[LELOUCH]
Yes, it will.
Or rather, it must
change the world.
[KALLEN]
But...!
[LELOUCH]
Will there be sacrifices?
Not only just soldiers,
but the innocent as well.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] And yet, because
of all these things,
we've no choice but
to continue on...
...no matter the cost.
Even if people see
us as cowards...
We have to prevail!
If that means more
blood will be shed,
so be it. We've spilled
so much to get here,
we can't let it be in vain...
But I won't force you, Kallen.
If you wish to turn back,
now is the time.
[gasps]
I've made my choice. I'll
follow you to the very end.
I'm grateful, Kallen.
[gasps]
[LELOUCH]
Yes. You saved me today.
Thank you.
C.C., I need you. I do.
What am I doing?
I just can't afford to
make the same mistake here
all over again here.
[DALTON]
It's time.
Commence with the operation!
[MARINE A] All underwater
units, hit the water!
Dive, dive, dive!
[MARINE B]
Supression Team, you are cleared
for cartegory C weaponry.
[MARINE OFFICER]
Our unit'll be covering them
from the shore. Careful though,
we want that tanker
in one piece.
Understood, my lord.
[MARINE D] Once torpedo
attack is confirmed,
all units go to weapons free.
Repeat. Weapons free.
Oh my god! Terrorists?!
It looks like it's starting.
Zero...
You wanna move out or what?
Hey! Do you read me?
They're closing in
on the JLF! Come in!
[ZERO]
We have to hold.
Huh?
[ZERO] Cornelia moved
faster than expected.
If we go now, we'll
die along with them.
[MARINE OFFICER]
Commence support fire.
All units restricted to
micro round ordinance only.
Be careful not to set off
that liquid Sakuradite!
[ITAGAKI]
Damn those Britannians!
When the hell did
they get here?!
Enemy units! They're
coming from the water!
Itagaki!
[MARINE A]
Two-oh-two! Five-oh-three!
Focus fire at nine o'clock!
This isn't battle. This is
wholesale slaughter!
[CECILE]
Officer Kururugi.
Go ahead.
I certainly know this
must be hard for you,
but you're a soldier,
remember that.
[SUZAKU]
Right. I understand.
How could they have
found us?! Where's Tohdoh?!
[JLF SOLDIER D]
We can't locate him!
Or the Holy Swords!
[KATASE]
What about Kyoto?!
They said they would send help!
[JLF SOLDIER D]
Yes, sir, but we have no way
of contacting them now!
So they're just gonna sit back
and watch us die here?!
[JLF SOLDIER E] We surrender!
Please, cease fire!
This is the
Japan Liberation Front!
I reapeat! We surrender!
Sir, they're issuing a surrender
over an open channel!
[MARINE OFFICER]
Ignore it.
Yes, but, sir!
[MARINE OFFICER]
You see?
They were just buying time.
Now, carry out your orders.
Lulu just couldn't be a member
of the Black Knights, could he?
[OHGI] Ugh! Dammit!
It'll be too late soon!
When does Zero plan to move?!
I just hope that he
isn't just doing all this
to honor some childish
notion of justice.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[OHGI] The Knightmares
are boarding the ship!
[ZERO]
I see.
That leaves only one way out.
They have to be careful around
that precious Sakuradite.
[OHGI]
Zero! If we don't hurry...
Very well then. Go ahead...
What the hell is going on?!
[CORNELIA]
I can't believe this idiocy!
They blew up the
liquid Sakuradite?!
[ZERO] Just what you'd
expect of the JLF.
Choosing to take the
Britanians out with them!
Suicide? But they
never mentioned--!
[ZERO] We're going to
rush Cornelia's position
head on!
Forget about everything else!
All that matters is
achieving our goal!
If you want to avenge the JLF,
then capture Cornelia
and show them our
strength and determination!
Right...!
[OHGI] This is like
Narita all over again!
[DIETHARD]
It's outstanding!
[OHGI]
Hey! Get back here!
[DIETHARD]
The JLF was just bait!
Their command is wide open now.
Heh. One of the oldest
tricks in the book...
Where're you going?! Hey!
[DIETHARD]
It makes perfect sense!
He wanted to cripple
his enemy's defenses,
using the Liberation Front
as a living trap!
He's excellent
material, this Zero.
He's chaos incarnate! More...
Show me more of your genius!
Let your ego engulf the world!
[laughing]
[MARINE A]
E-Enemy attack?!
[MARINE B]
Two-zero-four, signal lost!
Erickson, form up
with three-zero-eight!
Provide support!
[MARINE C]
All units, status report!
I repeat, what is your status?!
Why would the
general kill himself?
It doesn't make any sense...
[SUZAKU gasps]
The main force...!
Could they have used
the tanker as a decoy?!
[DALTON] Mount up now and
form a defensive line,
on the double!
How did they know we were here?!
Your Highness!
[ZERO] Knock their
Knightmares into the sea
before the pilots can mount!
Guren Mark-Two, you're with me!
Yes, sir!
[GUILFORD] Your Highness!
We can handle this!
Quiet!
How many times do you
think I'll allow them
to mock me?!
I haven't even powered on!
Do you think you can best
me in Knightmare combat?!
[CORNELIA]
That new model again?!
[ZERO] I'll smash your
hatch and drag you out...
Cornelia!
[ZERO grunts]
[LELOUCH gasps]
Shirley?!
Zero!
Your methods are not
going to change anything!
You're focused on goals,
and don't understand
the pain of others!
Zero!
[CORNELIA]
This is payback for Narita!
[ZERO] Well, if it isn't
the knight in shining armor!
These are people's lives
you're playing with!
You're nothing but a murderer!
[ZERO grunts]
[LELOUCH]
Why?!
Why do you keep
getting in my way?!
spilling people's blood
without meaning?!
[LELOUCH]
If it wasn't for you...!
Because of you...!
[ZERO groaning]
Zero... This is the end result.
[CORNELIA]
Lancelot, behind you!
[gasps]
Get the hell away from him!
[SHIRLEY]
Is this Zero's? So...
...then, with this...
I'll repay you... for my father!
[ZERO grunts]
[gasps]
[LELOUCH] The best laid
plans often fall apart.
Doubts can arise at any time.
My heart grows heavier,
little by little...
Is this the foundation
for the future?
Or merely stumbling
blocks from the past?
The answers that I seek...
...lie within me.